[wind howling]
- This snow--What's going on?
- VILLAGER: Miss Emilia!
- [gasps]
[villagers murmuring]
EMILIA: I don't understand!
Where did
this snowstorm come from?
- It only started to fall
a few moments ago,
but it's already started
to pile up quite heavily.
And of course we can't evacuate.
Still, we've escaped
the worst of it thanks to this.
- Thank goodness,
but who made it for all of you?
- Huh?
- [murmuring]
- So are you saying
you aren't the one
who's responsible for this?
- You thought I made it? Mm-mmm.
- But that spirit said
if we wanted to thank someone,
it should be Miss Emilia.
Actually they said, "Lia."
- It was Puck.
[gasps]
- [ice crackles]
- [gasps]
PUCK: What are you waiting for?
You still have
a job to do, Lia.
- [grunts]
Everyone,
I've finished the last trial.
However, I think
it's too dangerous
to move at the moment,
so for now,
take refuge in the graveyard.
- You there.
- [grunts]
- Would you oversee that for me?
- [grunts] Right!
ELDER: And what is it
that you'll be doing?
- It seems...
I'm expected
to head in that direction.
Could you wait for me?
- [murmuring]
- We'll keep the vow we made
before you started the trial.
Stay safe, Miss Emilia,
and be careful.
[embers crackling]
[sentimental music playing]
- Why, Ram?
PUCK: You lost your temper
when she burned the book.
That's not like you.
But she was prepared
for what would happen,
'cause she's strong.
- Ram...
why did you...
- Please listen.
Master Roswaal, I love you.
PUCK: You lost this time,
Roswaal,
and she got
just what she wanted.
She crossed that fine line.
Soon Lia will finish her trial,
and that book of yours is gone.
While your attachment to that
thing was pretty impressive,
you still--[gasps]
Snow?
No, it can't be.
[gasps]
You got me, didn't you?
You inscribed the spell
that calls the snow clouds
before the battle even began.
It'll fall,
then end up
the way Subaru was afraid of.
I'm gonna go
and try to delay that.
Roswaal, you really amaze me.
You're quite a magician.
As far as I know,
there's no human alive
as skilled at magic as you.
But no matter how far you go,
you're still a human.
You're never going to be
like that devil.
I made snow fall
as the Tome of Wisdom dictated.
What do I do now?
[no audible dialogue]
Dear Ram.
That's it. Yes.
Teacher, talk to me.
Say something.
Please, tell me!
What should I do, Teacher?!
Answer me!
[shudders]
I still--I don't know anything.
Please, give me
your guidance again.
[wind howling]
- Mana's swirling around here.
Could this be what's
making all the snow fall?
[shards clattering]
Huh?
Puck is waiting. I have to go.
[gasps]
Miss Ryuzu?
- Miss Emilia. Why are you here?
- There are this many of you?
Making you all must have been
so rough on your poor mother.
- Explanations
regarding us clones can wait.
Please, for now,
I just need you to stop me!
- Sorry, but I don't know
what you mean. [gasps]
You're Miss Shima, right?
- Miss Emilia,
the very fact that you are here
must mean
you have overcome the trial.
It seems
Young Gar's wager was correct.
- Is that Miss Ryuzu
inside the magic crystal?
Are you here to get her out?
Should we take her
to the graveyard together?
[breeze echoes]
- [Echidna's voice]
Unbelievable. You see this,
and that's the very first thing
you think of?
- [grunts] It's fine.
If we make a sled
and then put her on it,
I'm sure we can all manage
to pull her there.
- [normal voice] Your
kind gesture is appreciated,
But the reason I came here
is to fulfill my role
along with my ancestor,
who lies dormant
within this crystal.
- Fulfill your role?
- Indeed.
This crystal is the core
of the barrier
surrounding the Sanctuary.
Your recent activity
has undone its spell.
Once the core is gone,
the Sanctuary's role
will be completed,
and it will be liberated.
If it is gone, of course.
- U-Um, does that
have to happen right now?
I'm not sure if you've noticed,
but it's snowing
really hard outside,
so maybe you could just--
- In the event
that this facility is destroyed
and the one who runs it is lost,
the damage will be irreparable.
We are the key
to preventing that.
- [gasps]
- Miss Emilia, take this.
Hold on. Is this Puck?
- The great spirit
visited here in advance
and managed to delay
the spell's activation.
His actions will save everyone,
though his strength
was exhausted.
- And he also made
that wall of ice
to protect everyone
in the Sanctuary from the snow,
then pushed himself to the brink
like this so I knew.
Oh, Puck, how many other
impossible things did you do?
- He lent us aid in many
forms,
all of which are appreciated.
Now that we have been given
this opportunity,
it is my responsibility
to fulfill our role.
RYUZU MEYER: Yes,
I understand that, but still--
- Our beloved grandson Garf has
been with me for ten years now.
At this very moment,
he is risking his life,
giving his all
to make it to the outside.
I will do everything
I can to try and help.
My sisters made from half of me,
I must ask you to please watch
and see where it takes him.
- [crying]
- Leave the rest to me.
I'll take care of it.
- [chuckles]
Seems you have grown
a shocking amount
in just half a day's time.
This is the one thing old folks
like me take sheer pleasure in.
[no audible dialogue]
[energy surges]
[Ryuzu Meyer crying]
EMILIA: Let's go, Ryuzu.
- Hmm?
- Dry your tears.
There's something
that we need to do.
- What is it, Miss Emilia?
- A wish has been
entrusted to me,
and now I need to fulfill it,
which means all your crying
will have to wait.
People I love told me that,
and it was always with a
smile.
- [sighs]
[gasps]
- Now I'd like
for you to tell me
where to find Ram and Roswaal.
- [sighs]
[grunts]
[wind howling]
EMILIA: Ram! Roswaal!
Hey! Come on, Roswaal.
Snap out of it.
You can't stay here!
You need to get out of the cold!
- [gasping]
Ram?
Hey! Ram?
- [sighs]
- [gasps] She's alive!
It's all right.
There's still time!
Did you hear me?
You're helping her, aren't you?
Listen, right now I need you
to pick her up and come with
me.
I'll do what I can,
so don't give up!
- It's too late.
- Huh?
- It won't matter.
[tense music playing]
- Don't you dare
say things like that!
What do you mean by,
"It won't matter"?
Of course it does,
so you need to get up now!
Don't lose hope and think
that there's nothing we can do!
For me, Ram, and for you...
every single thing matters,
everything counts, understand?!
- [gasps]
- I did it.
I completed the trial!
The past
that I was afraid to face,
the happy present
that could have happened,
the awful future
that might come true one day,
I saw everything!
Even so, I still pressed on!
I won't give up!
And now I finally
get to move forward!
What are you doing?!
Hey! When you're
talking with someone,
you need to look them
in the eye!
I refuse to let people
say they're losing heart.
As long as you're
still breathing,
things have meaning.
They're important!
Those trials made me
more determined than ever.
I'm never giving up
on anyone again!
[dramatic music playing]
[Great Rabbits chittering]
- Why are they here?
Maybe they're following me
because I'm a witch.
Or is it 'cause Puck's with me?
[grunts]
- [chittering]
- Get Roswaal and Ram
out of here.
[footsteps rumbling]
When we get back
to the graveyard,
I'll do whatever it takes
to protect all of you!
[flames crackling]
BEATRICE: I began waiting
for "that person"
after I lost Ryuzu,
and the Sanctuary
was established in her place.
That event happened
in a matter of moments,
but it still haunts me
to this day.
[sentimental music playing]
ECHIDNA: Listen to me, Beatrice.
I'm leaving you in charge
of the library that's filled
with my knowledge.
This is
a crucial responsibility.
I want you
to continue protecting it
until the time comes.
- Huh?
- I know!
We'll call it
the forbidden library.
And over there, I'll write
down
all of the collected wisdom
that I possess and then
store it for safekeeping.
- W-Wait.
- I want you to build it
inside Roswaal's mansion.
I'm confident he'll be honored
and will even help you.
- Wait a minute, I suppose!
Wh-What's all this
about a forbidden library?
I don't know
what you're talking about!
I just want to stay with you.
- I'm sorry, little one,
but you won't be of any
help
against an enemy
Roswaal can't handle.
We each share
an immense amount of knowledge.
What happens if we both die?
I feel rather obligated
to pass it down.
- Hold on. Are you telling me
my power exists
for this very moment?
And you knew it
from the beginning?
- [grunts]
- [gasps]
What's this?
- Though it's a bit incomplete,
this is a replica
of the Tome of Wisdom
that
the Authority granted to
me.
It should serve
as a simple guide
to its owner's future, anyway.
- [gasps]
- There are two copies.
This one is meant for you,
and I gave the other to Roswaal.
I'm sorry,
but please understand.
We should discuss
the time frame.
In the unlikely event
that I don't return,
someone who's deemed
suitable for inheriting
my wealth of knowledge
will come for you.
- What kind of "someone"
will this be?
- For now, let's just
call them "that person."
Until then, you must wait.
Your compliance is
my final request of you.
- [sighs]
- Betty...
- [crying]
- I want you
to grow up healthy, at least.
[closing door echoes]
- With that,
I moved to Roswaal's mansion,
just as Mother
had instructed me to.
I built the forbidden library
and became its guardian.
- [hinges creak]
- At some point,
Roswaal started stopping by
on a fairly regular basis.
- Hello, and good day.
I thought I'd drop by again
for another visit.
Replication of the soul...
- The information he sought
was within the books.
- ...inside a vessel.
- During these times,
we rarely spoke to each other.
- Pleased to meet you,
Miss Beatrice.
It's an honor.
I've heard all about you
from my predecessor.
And I understand,
so don't worry.
As the current Roswaal,
Roswaal B. Mathers,
I will inherit your role
and your debt to your mother.
- As time passed,
control over the mansion
was handed down
from one Roswaal to the next.
Apart from those brief moments,
nothing of note happened
for the next 400 years.
A few people found their way
to the forbidden library
and attempted
to take me out of it...
but that never happened.
When I was reunited
with the one I looked up to
as a big brother,
my heart sang
for the first time in ages.
But I soon came to realize
that the two of us
weren't the same.
Driven by envy and jealousy,
I buried my emotions
and stopped talking
so I wouldn't hurt
the half-devil girl
who was always with him.
And then...
- The first NPC found!
- Suddenly, without hesitation,
an outsider walked in
with dirty shoes on.
- What's up?
- For whatever reason,
he stayed in the mansion.
- Beako!
- And he was different
from the others
who came
to the forbidden library.
At times, I even thought
he might be "that person,"
as Mother had mentioned to me.
[no audible dialogue]
The fear
that the faint hope I had
would end up betrayed
began to consume me,
so I sent him to the Sanctuary
according to Roswaal's plans.
Then Roswaal himself
departed for the Sanctuary,
saying that he was off
to see the Witch of Greed,
and I realized he intended
to settle the score.
What about me, then,
a blank book, a promised savior
who never came for me?
I finally admitted to myself
"that person" wasn't going
to show up. They never were.
I've known that
for a long time.
And yet...
- I'm getting you
out of here, Beatrice.
We're heading into the sunlight
to play in the mud
until that dress of yours
is covered in it!
- I-If you're
really "that person,"
then would you be
"that person" for me, too?
- Have you lost your mind?
There's no way I could be
whoever "that per--"
[yelps]
- I'm just so tired.
- [flames crackling]
- [doors opening]
- [winces]
Damn it, Beako!
Where the hell are you?!
[tense music playing]
[no audible dialogue]
- Oh, well.
- Guess I should just--
- [door opens]
- I finally made it back here!
Listen, idiot,
you've got some nerve--
Canasta!
- You're the one
who ended our conversation.
And now you--
How impudent you are, I suppose.
- [door opens]
- Cut that out already!
You're so childish! If
you
jump straight to
violence...
- You need to stop
moving your mouth and go!
- [grunting]
There! I made it.
- You don't know
when to give up.
- Until you actually
shut me out for real,
I'll just come back
over and over again!
- [gasps]
I am shutting you out for--
- Now don't give me that!
Because if you were
serious,
there's no way I'd be able
to keep on showin' up
all these times!
So stop lying!
You're just putting up a front!
- [gasps]
[sighs]
You--You said...
you're not "that person"!
I asked you, and you told me
to my face that you're not!
That's what you said, so don't
even try to deny it, I suppose!
[crying] If you
were "that person..."
if you'd said you were,
even if it wasn't true,
I still would have believed you.
Even knowing it was a lie,
I would have had to believe you!
- B-Beatrice...
- But you, you said you weren't,
I suppose!
You thought I'd lost my mind
and called me a fool,
didn't you?!
Well, maybe you're right.
I am a fool
who can't bring herself
to ignore
a 400-year-old promise.
So just forget it!
No matter what you say,
it's over, I suppose!
[energy surging]
- I'm...
I'm not whoever
"that person" is,
and that's the truth.
- [gasps]
- But...
even so, I want to stay
with you, Beatrice.
I mean it.
- [gasping]
- I want to be near you
so you won't feel sad,
because I know how kind you are.
- [gasps]
[energy warbling]
- What the...
[rumbling]
- [gasping]
Beatrice, no!
Beatrice!
[no audible dialogue]
- [groans]
The entrance to the mansion.
Is she telling me
to leave here for good?
If every door
in this entire place burns down,
does that mean
her forbidden library will be...
- Goodbye, and farewell.
- "Goodbye, and farewell,"
my ass!
You think I'm just gonna give
up
and let you end it like that?!
[grunting]
There aren't any doors left.
[gasps]
Wait. That's right.
[rumbling]
Eh?
[door rattling]
Beatrice, if you can hear me,
then listen up.
There aren't
any other ones left.
This is the last of them.
If I open it...
I'll probably die.
[rumbling]
[winces]
Come on, Beatrice.
I have faith in you!
[rumbling fades]
[gasps]
[debris clattering]
- You're such an idiot.
- After all this,
that's the first thing you say?
- Well, it's true, I suppose.
We find ourselves
in a stalemate now.
I couldn't ask
for much more at this point.
The promise made with Mother's
been fully realized, I suppose.
- If that's true...
then I want you
to hear me out until the end.
- You have to help me.
Beatrice, please save me.
- Wait. What?
- I thought about all sorts
of cool things to say to you,
like how I was gonna stop you
from ever feeling lonely
again,
but honestly each one
just sounded more contrived
than the next.
[energy crackling]
You don't need me
to try and rescue you.
In fact, I'm pretty sure
you don't need my help at all.
You're strong, smart,
resilient, cute.
As far as I'm concerned,
that makes you
more than well-equipped
to survive on your own,
which means saying
I'd save you or help you out
wasn't enough,
not by a long shot.
Even so, with every one of those
amazing qualities you have,
you were afraid
to go on living alone.
You were hurting and sad,
weren't you?
So I completely understand.
No one could blame you
for clinging to the idea
of "that person."
- I-Is that so?
And now you think you
can
just reject how I'm
feeling?
What do you know about me?!
[crying]
- Much more than you think.
I know how sweet you really are,
how you're someone
who'd hold a person's hand
and do your best
to calm them down
when they're having nightmares.
- Don't talk as if you know me.
- I don't really have
any strength,
so I can't be
of much help to you.
But I don't want
to leave you all alone,
which means
I've only got one choice now,
and that's to just hang on tight
and keep begging.
- [gasps]
- Uh...
[winces]
I need your help,
so please say
that you'll take my hand.
Without you,
I'd be too depressed
to go on living. Please.
- [crying]
That's not fair.
[sobs] It's not fair of you
when you ask me like that.
You said--
you said that you're
not "that person."
You completely rejected me.
[crying]
And yet...
I've been alone for 400 years.
Even if I decided
to take your hand,
you'll just die soon anyway.
Compared to mine,
a human's life is over
in the blink of an eye.
What's the use
in clinging to that if you...
- But I'll still be able
to hold your hand right now
and again tomorrow.
- [crying]
- I'll hold it the next day
and the day after that!
I can't make it 400 years,
but what time I have, I want
to spend it together with you.
[energy crackling]
And even if it can't be forever,
I can treasure you
with all that I've got,
with all the moments I've got!
So then, what do you say?
Choose me, Beatrice.
- But you're not--
you're not "that person."
- No.
I'm no one but me,
Subaru Natsuki.
Forget about this torch you're
carrying for some stranger
you wouldn't even recognize
in the first place.
- [gasps]
- Come on. Instead of fearing
a goodbye that might or
might not happen, live with me
through a guaranteed lifetime
of tomorrows.
You'll never be bored.
I'm pretty weak,
which means I can be a handful.
And as caring as I know you are,
you'll stay busy
looking after me.
I'll keep you so occupied,
you won't ever have time to
think about being sad or lonely.
- [crying]
- Choose me, Beatrice.
I beg you.
- But at some point,
you'll go away forever.
- That's just the way it is.
The future you're so afraid of
is gonna come sooner or later.
Even so...
- But you'll die
and leave me behind.
- Even so, let's be together!
We'll do things side by
side
and live with one
another!
Let's try and make
enough
memories to last a
lifetime,
one where you can finally say
you've had fun!
Take back those empty 400 years
you've had with interest,
'cause you
definitely deserve it.
- [crying] I can't get past...
knowing that you'll die,
that I'll be alone!
- That's true.
And for somebody like you
who'll live for ages,
your time with me
might feel like an instant,
so I'll engrave each one
of our memories into your soul!
I swear it'll be worth it.
Someday, you'll look back
at all the moments spent with me
and think to yourself,
"Subaru Natsuki
"was a guy so memorable
that even after an eternity,
I still can't forget him!"
[rumbling]
Take my hand,
and choose me, Beatrice!
- [crying]
- You want someone to get you
out of here, don't you?!
Isn't that the reason why you
sat right in front of this
door
for hundreds of years?!
[energy shattering]
[flames crackling]
["Believe in You" playing]
- [gasps]
[sighs]
- Otto, look!
- [wincing]
- Over there!
- [gasps]
[singing in Japanese]
BEATRICE: Subaru.
SUBARU: Mm-hmm?
- Subaru. Subaru.
- Uh-huh, that's it.
- Subaru! Subaru!
Subaru! Subaru!
- You finally
called me by my name.
- ♪ I believe,
I believe in you ♪
[singing in Japanese]
- [panting]
I absolutely will not...
let anything or anybody
be lost again!
Mother and Geuse,
everyone from today...
and the words he wrote,
as long as I remember
each and every one of them,
I won't ever give up!
SUBARU: Come on.
You don't have to push yourself
that hard, Mili.
[snow crunches]
- [gasps]
So you can relax
and just leave
the rest to me now.
This is a little payback
for my first battle.
- I'm sorry...
but I'm not really sure
what you mean.
- [chuckles]
[song ends]
[wind howling]
BEATRICE: Don't blame me
for whatever may happen next.
SUBARU: I won't.
We'll make it all work out.
You and me
are gonna face this together!