[birds chirping]
- Uh...
- Come on now! Don't ignore me!
- [Subaru yelps]
- [grunting]
- [groaning]
- [laughs]
Hey, what's the matter?
You train daily and still lose
to a middle-aged man?
Huh? No, no, no, no!
- [grunts] You're getting old...
- [groaning]
- if you didn't see
that counter coming, Pops!
I'm about to win by decis--
- Hey! Wait!
- [laughs]
- No fair flipping me back over!
- Are you ready to give up?
- Cut it out! Stop it! Stop!
- Then you better say uncle!
- Excuse me. Come on, you guys.
- Uh...
- I'm getting hungry,
so I'd like
to have some breakfast.
Could you two wrap this up now?
- Oh, whoops.
Sorry about that.
Got a little carried away
with my one-on-one time
with Subaru.
You could have started
without us, though.
- But why should I do that
when the whole family
could sit down together?
- You know,
you're absolutely right, honey.
Really sorry.
That's my wife for you!
- Come on.
It's time for breakfast.
I started feeling adventurous,
so I made
something special just for you.
- Well, would you look at that?
Bet you weren't expecting
a mountain of peas.
- Hey, Mom, I appreciate it,
but why are there
so many of these things?
- It's not good
to be picky about your food,
so I thought this might be
a good chance
to get you over that.
- It's not like this is
a special day or anything.
- What do you mean by chance?
- Very naive of you, son,
and that's because today--
no, every moment of every day
is a precious,
once-in-a-lifetime opportunity
to make a positive change.
SUBARU: Doesn't matter now,
so...
it's time to eat.
- Don't be shy, and dig in.
SUBARU: You know,
I've always wondered
about this mix
of Japanese and Western dishes.
- I like wakame seaweed
in my miso soup
and strawberry jam on my toast.
Yummy.
- Huh?
[sighs]
What are we gonna do with this?
We can't just keep on
passing it around.
MOM: Well, I hate peas, so one
of you will have to eat it.
- [gasps] And you were trying
to get me to be less picky?!
- Don't get the wrong idea,
though.
I hate all foods
that are tiny and round.
Peas just happen
to fit that category.
- Oh, I didn't have
the wrong idea!
If anything,
now I have even more doubts!
The husband should take
responsibility for his wife.
- [chuckles] Listen.
Families that get along
as well as ours does
are rare these days.
What I'm saying
is you and your mother
hate exactly
the same things I do.
- Then this gigantic
mound of peas
was never gonna make
anyone happy, now, was it?
- I'll turn it into something
we all love, pilaf!
[dramatic music plays]
- I can't even stand
the sight of it.
[both groan]
- Subaru?
Right.
- [claps]
- [groans]
- Thank you
for that bountiful feast!
- Not a problem! Now, let's
get the dishes to the sink,
and after that, we'll
race
to school to help
digestion!
- Stop trying to turn this
into a scenario
that ends with me
going off to school, okay?
I'm heading back to bed.
[groans] Ow.
PARENTS: Subaru?
- It's nothing.
[footsteps recede]
[footsteps shuffling]
[panting]
What the hell?
Why do I feel so weird
all of a sudden?
[ticking]
[panting]
Once it gets past 8:00,
it's over.
[gasping]
[ticks echoing]
[ticking fades]
[sighs]
[normal ticking]
I won't make it to school
on time now,
so there's no other choice.
It's a done deal.
[groans]
What the hell is this?
That's always
calmed it down before.
[groans]
- [whoops] Hee hee!
Hey, mind if I join you, Subaru?
- What's the point of asking
if you walk in
before I can answer?
- Oh, lighten up.
There's no need for that
between two guys
as tight as you and--
Oh, wait! You're right!
I'm sorry.
I forgot you're a teenager.
- I'll leave and come back.
- Ah, too late now.
It doesn't matter.
What do you want?
Oh, nothing.
So tell me,
is there a girl you like?
- Are you serious?!
- [scoffs] You're no fun at all.
- Come on.
What do you really want?
Hmm. Well, let's see.
The weather
is pretty nice, so...
Let's go have an awesome
father-son talk outside, okay?
[birds chirping]
Man, what's with everybody?
They happen to see me
on my day off,
and they all assume
I lost my job.
Hey, what's with
the gloomy face?
Don't be like that.
It's a beautiful morning.
- It's your own fault
for dragging me out here.
- Why so suspicious?
Look, I'm not going
to tell you anything scary.
It's more
of a father-son subject.
- Ah, tell me more.
I can't wait.
- Ken, my boy!
Haven't seen you in a while.
Oh, hold on.
Don't tell me that's...
- Uh-huh. This is my son.
Or as I like to affectionately
call him, "my pride and joy."
- Ah! It seems I was right.
He looks so much like you did
back when you were--
Actually, no.
Take after your mom?
- Uh, well--[chuckles]
That's what people say.
Around the eyes, especially.
- Of course. Time does fly.
It's hard to believe
you're old enough
to have a son who's that age.
Come to think of it,
today's Monday, right?
Shouldn't you be
in school now, young man?
[groans]
Sorry. Gotta go.
- Eh, hey! What's wrong?
My apologies.
We'll both stop by again
when we have time to chat.
- Sounds good.
Looks like I said
something I shouldn't have.
Please tell him I'm sorry,
would you?
KEN: Oh, no.
That won't be necessary.
It's up to him to deal
with this on his own now.
[can thumps]
Here.
A tasty, ice-cold cola
packed with love.
[Ken sighs]
- You really thought
I didn't see that coming?
I know how you are.
Ugh. My hands are all sticky.
- [sighs]
- Well...
are you feeling any better now?
- It's kinda hard to say.
[groans]
- You look like you really
aren't feeling too great, son.
Are you ready to head back home?
Just hop on. I can carry you.
- No. Don't worry about it.
There's no need to do that.
It would only be the same
back there, anyway.
- So, uh, listen, Subaru,
not to change
the subject on you,
but is there a girl
that you like?
- [groaning in pain]
EMILIA: Subaru.
- [gasps] Huh?
Uh...
KEN: What's up?
- Did somebody just say my name?
- Don't think so.
If not, then what was it
that I just heard?
- So? Come on now.
Is there a girl you like?
- Why are you
going on about that?
Stop beating
around the bush, okay?
Come out and ask me.
"Why didn't you
head off to school today?"
It's easy.
- Hey, excuse me
for trying to be considerate
for once in my life.
Well, I suppose
you could see through me anyway,
since that is the thing
I wanted to talk about.
- [gasps]
I know it's disrespectful
to you and Mom.
- Ah, there's no need
to feel that way.
I've got a vague sense
that you have your own reasons.
And even if you don't,
I'm prepared to brush it off
as something
I can't do anything about.
Now, I can't really speak
for the rest of the world,
but personally I don't believe
school is the be-all-end-all.
It's not a big deal.
- But why?
- Hmm?
Why did you suddenly decide
to tell me
all of this stuff right now?
What's the occasion?
Today's not
a special day or anything.
Unless it's secretly
Mountain of Peas Day.
- Well, your bowl was certainly
full of those things, wasn't it?
I'm not really sure why.
I guess the look on your face
this morning
just seemed a little better.
- [gasps] My face looked better?
- [chuckles]
The expression on it, I mean.
Of course you still
do look like a bad guy,
thanks to those angry eyes
you inherited from your
mom.
- [sighs] You're crazy.
Nothing about me has changed.
That's how I want it, okay?
And that's how I'll--
[groaning]
- Hey, are you all right?
You look like
you're really hurting!
- Just tell me what's wrong.
- [heart beating]
- Subaru, please.
- [gasping]
EMILIA: It's been rough,
hasn't it?
- [gasps]
[heartbeat stops]
[music playing]
[gasps]
- Thank you, Subaru.
- Who are you?
- Thank you for saving me.
- Wait. What?
What's going on here?
- Subaru...
- Who are you?
Who are you?
Who are you? Who are you...
- may the blessing
of the spirits be with you.
- Who are you? [gasps]
[heart beating]
- I think you're much more
amazing than I could ever be.
Tell me,
why do you always save me?
- [gasps]
- [heartbeat stops]
- [music continues]
Sorry. I'm all right now.
KEN: You sure?
Okay, as long
as you feel better.
But don't worry me
so much, you hear?
- Yeah. I'm sorry.
And about what you asked me...
there is one, a girl I like,
so now I just know I'll be fine.
[wind blowing]
SUBARU: I remember
everything now,
what I was so freaked out about
and why I was cowering in fear.
No, that's not right.
I already knew all of it,
but even so,
I pretended I didn't see it.
I guess I just wanted you
and Mom to call out my weakness
since I was
the only one in pain,
to tell me
what a small person I am,
that I'm an idiot
who's never good enough
and a self-righteous scumbag.
I wanted you both to beat that
into me and make me give up.
'Cause, you know,
I've always had this way
of somehow managing
to squeak through anything,
like schoolwork and sports,
for instance.
[music playing]
CROWD: Oh, yeah.
You're definitely his kid.
SUBARU: But somewhere
along the way,
I stopped being the best
at things
I always used to excel at.
What used to be my best
grew smaller and smaller.
I started thinking
it was all pointless,
that it made no sense.
Working my hardest at school
seemed stupid.
And what's the big deal
about being a fast runner?
Making everyone laugh
seemed way cooler to me,
and I was way better at it.
CROWD: Oh, yeah.
You're definitely his kid!
SUBARU: And I quickly learned
that if I kept that up,
I'd always have to do
something even bigger
the next time around.
Can't have people
think I'm boring.
I figured I could do anything.
I made everybody think
I would do anything...
so the stuff I did
ended up being
progressively dumber.
I was out of control.
I wasn't thinking.
I knew they were
a bunch of idiots.
I wanted them to believe
that they couldn't have
this much fun without me,
that we'd break up the boring
times doing pointless crap
for fun with or without regrets,
so I decided
I'd set my sights higher.
But the next thing I knew,
after taking
a good look around...
I found there was
no one left but me.
It was right then and there
when I finally realized,
despite all my efforts
to be the center of attention,
there was nothing special
about me at all.
[faint overlapping chatter]
CROWD: Oh, yeah.
You're definitely his kid!
- From that moment on,
I just tried to be invisible,
doing my best not to stand out,
and that's how I made it
all through middle school.
But things changed after that.
Honestly, I really blew my
high school debut in a big way.
It was bound to happen, though.
I'd never had any real
relationships up to that point.
High school wasn't
gonna be any better.
And then one day,
it kind of hit me.
I just didn't want
to go to school at all.
Everything snowballed
from there.
I skipped school once a week,
then once every three days,
then every other day.
It didn't even
take me three months
before I had stopped
going there altogether.
But somehow,
no matter how pathetic I was,
you and Mom
just treated me the same way,
like it didn't make
any difference.
I think that's what
scared me most of all.
I wanted you to say,
"I don't love you,"
or, "I can't stand you,"
or maybe even,
"You are not my son."
I really hoped
you'd tell me that
and then throw me out.
I wanted you
to just make me give it all up.
But now...
REM: It's easy to give up,
but doing so doesn't suit you.
I love you, Subaru,
so very much.
Let's start here...
from square one.
No...
from zero!
My hero,
he's the greatest in the world.
- Subaru...
- Eh?
Huh?
- Father Head-butt!
- [groans]
- You see that, son?
That was my most loving
Father Head-butt,
- packed with all my rage!
- Hey, that was an ax kick,
not a head-butt! Ow!
You're right!
My leg goes up pretty high.
This is
just an observation here,
but you're kind of stupid,
aren't you?
- Uh, huh?
- A lot about what you said
bothers me,
but you know what's the worst?
You wanted me to hate
you,
so you tried to achieve
that
by playing hooky? How dumb!
If you want to get me
to throw you out,
then pick a more active
method!
Who would ditch their own kid
just because he retreated
into his shell, huh?!
You're so twisted,
you're on the fast track
to being an idiot!
And just so you know,
I'd be glad
to set you straight
by force if you want,
but it looks like you've
already been knocked down
and you've been able
to stand back up,
so there's no need
to do so, is there?
[laughs]
- You heard what I said.
I did find a girl that I like.
Actually there's another girl
who said she loves me,
despite all of the flaws
that I have.
And neither one of them
has any idea
that I'm the son
of Kenichi Natsuki.
In their eyes,
I'm just Subaru Natsuki,
nothing more, nothing less.
No, in all of their eyes,
just Subaru Natsuki.
I guess I finally
figured that out.
- What do you know?
It took you long enough.
You're really just now coming
around to saying all this
stuff?
I should whack you.
- You just whacked
my skull with your heel
- not even a few minutes ago!
- [chuckles] Sorry about that.
Still, I suppose this was
all my fault for not realizing
that you thought so highly
of your awesome dad.
Sorry. Looks like
I just ended up being
too big a part of your life.
- Yeah, I really don't want
to admit that's true,
- even though it is.
- Good talk.
That took a little weight
off my shoulders. [sighs]
Now we need to chat
about the future,
'cause we are
just getting started.
- Oh, sure. Um, sorry
for putting you through--
- If you really are
feeling sorry about everything,
all you gotta do from here
is take your time
making it up to us.
- [gasps]
- Okay?
Just try to take good care
of your mom and me
when we get old, all right, son?
- [gasps]
[crying]
I'm--I'm so sorry.
- Eh? Subaru?
- I'm sorry. I-I...
- [shudders]
- I can't.
I'm sorry.
I won't be able
to make anything up to you.
I'll probably
never see you again.
I'm sorry. I'm sorry.
I'm so sorry.
I'm sorry.
I'm so sorry!
- You know, no matter
how much time passes,
you're still
such a handful, son. Sheesh.
- [sobbing]
- All right, I still feel
like walking a little bit more,
so I think I'm gonna
take the long way home
to stretch my legs.
- Okay. I'll keep
heading this way, then.
[sighs]
- Hey, Subaru...
I'm sure you got a lot of things
going on right now, too,
so there's really only one thing
I want to say.
Just give it your all, son,
and do the best you can.
Got it?
- Yeah.
You can count on me, Dad.
Listen up!
My name is Subaru Natsuki,
son of Kenichi Natsuki!
I can do anything,
and I will do anything,
'cause your son's
just that awesome!
- Come on! I already know that.
I mean, you are half me,
after all,
- so it's in your blood.
- [chuckles]
[music playing]
Well, the student
Subaru Natsuki is complete.
What's it been already,
about three months or so?
- Hey! Are you feeling nervous?
Want to try out this new
mayonnaise on something?
- Nah, I'm not
in the mood right now.
- Suit yourself, then.
Guess I really
shouldn't be surprised.
After all, you don't actually
like mayonnaise that much.
- Huh?
- I mean, your dad and I
both like it quite a bit,
so I suppose you were
only sharing it with us.
- Uh, hang on.
What gives you that idea?
- Then, which would you choose,
the world or mayonnaise?
- Well, the world, obviously!
- Just as I thought.
- What's with
the self-satisfied smile?!
Look, anyone
who picks mayonnaise
doesn't do it
because they like mayonnaise!
They just hate the world,
all right?!
- [laughs]
Well, I suppose that's true.
- Anyway,
I should be heading out.
- You're leaving for school now?
Don't get me wrong. I'm glad,
but won't that give
a bad impression?
Why do today what you can
put off until tomorrow?
- Your son finally found
the motivation to do something!
Don't ruin it!
I'm too hard on everyone else
and easy on myself as it is!
Well, I must admit,
if you really were that way,
it would've meant
a whole lot less trouble for me,
and that, I can assure you
- Uh...
Hey, what's this about?!
Why are you following me?
Going from being a shut-in
to walking to school with my mom
is worse than a game penalty.
I'm not going
all the way to school.
Just to the convenience store,
all right?
It's been such a long time
since you and I walked together,
hasn't it?
- It has?
- What did you and your dad
talk about?
- Nothing special, really.
Just reliving the past
and stuff.
- Hmm. So reliving the past
somehow made you want
to go back to school, I guess?
- Well, I suppose
you could say that.
It gave me a chance
to look back on a few things
and sort them out.
Is that so, Subaru?
Then you've given up
on trying to be just like
your father in everything?
- Uh...
- You were always
an incredibly hard worker.
You could do so much
without even trying.
Since your dad was
into lots of different things,
you had
quite a few opportunities.
[laughs] Exhausting, isn't it?
- Mom, how much do you...
- [sighs]
You should know, Subaru,
parents keep a close eye
on their children,
more than they realize.
We're protective.
That goes for me, too.
I'm always watching you.
One time, when you were little,
I had to give you a suppository,
so I've even seen
your little heinie up close.
Whoa, T.M.I.!
It's nice going down
memory lane with you,
but don't tell me
everything, Mom.
- The back-and-forth
about mayonnaise,
as well as your reasons
for not going to school,
If there was anything at
all
I could have done for
you,
I gladly would have,
but no matter what I tried,
I felt like nothing was
going to make a difference.
However...
someone other
than your father and me
seems to have made a positive
impact on you, didn't they?
Whoever they are, I think
they did a wonderful thing.
We should be grateful to them.
- [chuckles]
Well, yeah, I agree.
That's why I'm able
to walk this path.
They really are
wonderful people.
I honestly don't deserve them.
- I see. But you won't give them
to anyone else, right?
- Aw, you better believe it.
'Cause whether
I'm good enough for them or not
isn't the issue at all.
If I had to give them away,
I'd make them mine,
even if I don't deserve them!
I'd just vow to make myself
worthy of them later on.
- Mm-hmm.
Oh, yeah.
You're definitely his kid.
- [gasps]
But am I--am I doing
everything that I can?
Am I living up
to all the expectations
of being his kid?
- [chuckles]
Don't worry about a thing.
'Cause after all,
half of everything
at the core of who you are
came from me,
so if you manage to become
even half as cool as your dad,
then you've filled your quota.
Just do whatever you need
to measure up to that
level.
And as for the other half,
that part can simply be Subaru.
- [gasps]
- Which means do your best
in your own way.
Be the best you that you can.
At least, that's what I think.
- The best in my own way, huh?
- Exactly. Though it's fine
if you want to be a bit
like your mom and dad
as you grow into yourself.
Well, I'm heading this way.
Will you be okay on your own?
- I'll be fine.
- I'm sure you will.
Give it your all, then.
[music playing]
- [clears throat]
Mom!
There's something I need to do!
I probably won't see you
for a long time!
It's kinda far away, too,
which means it'll be hard
to keep in touch!
Even so,
no matter where I might be,
I promise you
I'll be thinking of you guys,
and I'll never forget you.
- Subaru, I...
- I swear to you,
no matter what,
I'll always want to be your kid.
I'll try to never do anything
that makes me hate myself!
- My sweet boy.
- [gasps]
- It's okay.
Listen. I understand.
I know
what you're trying to say.
- Seriously? You really do?
How could you?
- Come now.
How could I know that?
Easy. Because I'm your mother,
of course.
- [crying]
I'm--I'm sorry, Mom.
I was never able
to do anything for you guys,
and now...
- Hey, we didn't have you
because we wanted you
to do something for us.
We had you because we wanted
to do something for you.
- [crying]
I'm acting like a little kid.
Pathetic.
- No, there's nothing wrong
with crying.
You can cry all you want.
As long as you smile
when you're done,
everything will be fine.
What matters isn't how you
start
or what happens in the middle.
It's all in how it ends.
- [sniffles]
- Nothing else matters,
just as long as everything
turns out okay in the end?
- Well, that's not exactly
how I meant for you to take it.
It's more like
a homework assignment from me.
- [grunts]
[inhales]
I'll be going. See you, then.
[music playing]
- Oh, that's right!
Subaru, wait! I almost forgot!
- Uh...
- Take care of yourself.
- [breathes deeply]
[music playing]
- Take care of yourself.
- [chuckles]
Thanks! I will!
[breathes deeply]
Okay.
- Well, look at you.
You're here
much earlier than I expected.
Welcome, Subaru.
So you've had some time
to confront your past.
Tell me, what did
that experience do for you?
[singing in Japanese]