[wind blowing]
PANDORA: Thank you.
I'm so glad you found it for me.
While I did manage
to find the seal on my own,
sadly, I couldn't find
the key anywhere.
- Okay. But...
wh-why are you here?
- [chuckles]
You seem so surprised.
You see, we've been
searching for this seal
for some time now, my dear,
so the fact that I'm
standing before you
is just a matter of course.
[music playing]
♪ This is the fate
that brought us here ♪
♪ Watch my long shot ♪
♪ Feel like I am falling
into the flame of lies ♪
♪ Tell me
what you want from me ♪
♪ Try not to step back
to where I still belong
♪ Looking for
the escape from fate ♪
♪ I will cross my fingers,
hoping not to be sacrificed ♪
[singing in Japanese]
♪ Getting the way ♪
♪ Get ready
for the time to come ♪
[singing in Japanese ]
♪ Trying to find the reason
why I'm standing here alone ♪
♪ Maybe it's already
too late to regain ♪
[singing in Japanese]
[whispers] Never again.
♪ But if I could
right my wrongs ♪
♪ And save you from our fate ♪
♪ It's not enough ♪
♪ It's not enough for me ♪
♪ To break ♪
♪ The rule of all this war ♪
♪ I will never wanna leave you ♪
♪ Never wanna lose you ♪
♪ We'll make it in the end ♪
♪ Never give up for real ♪
♪ I won't trust
someone else's lie ♪
♪ I love who I am ♪
- I don't get it.
Why, though? Why are you here?
- [gasps]
Oh, now I understand.
I suppose it's Bishop
Romanée-Conti and your mother
you truly want to know about.
There's no need to worry.
They're completely safe,
I assure you.
No harm has come
to either of them whatsoever.
- R-Really?
- Yes. Absolutely.
Neither the worshipers nor I
wish pain and suffering
on anybody.
The only thing that we're
interested in is the seal.
- [gasps] Then does that mean
when you're finished
with whatever you need it for,
you'll leave the forest?
And you'll go
without doing mean things
to the people who live here?
- Yes, of course.
We've no wish to make
any unnecessary sacrifices.
So please give me the key.
- The key?
- Yes. That's right, my child.
Since this seal is shaped
like a door with a giant lock,
naturally it can't
be opened without one.
- Uh...
- Furthermore,
I believe you're
in possession of it.
- I don't know what you mean!
- Hiding it from me would
be
quite an unwise decision.
- I-I'm not, I promise!
I really don't
know anything, okay?!
I've never even heard
of this key!
Nobody gave me one!
- Ah, is that so?
Then unfortunately,
I'll have to turn this entire
forest over 'til I find it.
- [gasps] Wait!
I'll do it!
I'll open the seal for you!
- You will?
Oh, I'm so relieved.
That's wonderful.
Then I was right.
You really had the key,
didn't you?
After all, it only makes sense.
You are the witch's daughter
obviously.
- Uh, I'm what?
Now to the seal,
if you don't mind.
As soon as the door
is unlocked and open,
we'll leave,
as I told you we would.
- [gasping]
- [heart beating]
- Simply focus on the lock.
Imagine you are its key.
- [gasping]
- [heart beating]
I'm--I'm the key.
- Am I to assume
that you see it now?
- You mean you can't see it?
Not at all,
though that's not surprising.
It's only given to the one
who's deemed qualified
to be in its possession.
- Well?
What are you waiting for?
Open it, and then
your wish will be granted.
FORTUNA: Emilia, promise me.
- I-I can't open it.
- Why not?
- Because I--
I made a promise.
- Did you? Well,
promises are very important.
Especially ones kept
with your mother, of course.
However...
sometimes a decision
has to be made,
even if means breaking
your word with another.
Knowing there are two hopes
before you, which do you seek?
- I'm confused.
What do you mean?
One is the hope
that you'll keep your promise,
while also getting us to leave
and overcoming this hardship.
The other is the hope
that by breaking your promise
and opening the seal,
you'll still somehow
resolve
all of this harmoniously.
Which path of fate
will you choose to walk?
The decision
lies on your shoulders.
- [crying]
I made a vow to my mother.
I'm going to keep my promise.
I have to. I love her!
[crying]
Mother.
- I understand, child.
She's your guiding light,
and you trust her
to the very end, don't you?
That has determined your answer.
It's the difficult decision
your soul has led you to,
and I thoroughly respect that.
- [gasps]
- But in turn,
I need for you
to accept my decision
that this seal will be opened...
- by any means necessary.
- [gasps]
- Pandora!
- It's dangerous to attack
without observing
your surround--
- [yells]
- [Emilia shrieks]
- Emilia?
Why are you here?
You should be
out of the forest by now!
- PANDORA: It's obvious.
- [gasps]
Do you not find it
a bit cruel to ask her why?
She came here
out of her concern for you,
because she wished to help you
and keep you safe from harm.
- [gasps]
- When each of you has
the same facial expression,
your resemblance
is even clearer.
Truly mother and daughter.
- I am not Emilia's mother,
you monster!
My sister-in-law
gave her that precious face!
- Ah, is that so?
I ask for your forgiveness,
then.
Touching.
Her real parents must be pleased
with the way
their daughter turned out.
- [gasps] You can say
what you want to me,
but don't you dare
speak of those two!
- Simply rampaging wildly
and refusing to talk
will only make you tired.
You should calm down
and listen.
We need to have
a discussion regarding--
- Keep your mouth shut!
- [yelps]
- No, Emilia!
Wait! I didn't mean to--
I would never...
- Your reality
is plagued with confusion.
Can't you direct that emotion
to the one you despise?
- [gasps]
- I would never tell you
to love all people
as you love your daughter,
but there are things
that can change
with a little empathy
and benevolence.
- That's ridiculous!
You're insane!
Who would listen
to some thing like you?!
- Then why not try another way?
Have your daughter
do what I wish
using your own words
instead of mine.
I've verified my suspicion
that she possesses the key,
but she hasn't shown any desire
to try and open the door,
because she wishes
to keep her oath with you.
- [gasps]
- [whimpers]
- Well, I'll promise you this.
If the seal is finally opened,
then we'll leave this forest
and do nothing further.
"Promise" is
such a nice word, isn't it?
- I'm so sorry, Emilia,
sorry for putting you
through all this.
- Did you come here alone?
Where's Archi?
- I'm not sure.
He told me to run
toward the white flowers
between the trees.
[no audible dialogue]
So I did!
I ran and didn't look back!
- [gasps]
Emilia...
I'm proud of you.
Thank you for having the courage
to keep your word to me.
What a good girl.
- Mother!
Mother, I--
I'm sorry. I just wanted--
- None of that now.
I'm so proud of you, sweetheart.
You're such a treasure to me.
- What beautiful, motherly love.
I'm deeply moved by it.
How special.
I feel lucky to see
such a display of emotion.
FORTUNA: I won't open the seal,
and I won't let you have her.
Now get ready.
It's time to turn into
an ice statue and die!
- I finally caught up to you!
Come on!
FORTUNA: Geuse!
- Miss Fortuna!
- [gasps]
Al Huma!
- Unseen Hand!
- [gasps]
Mother?
[gags]
- [gasps]
- [gags]
GEUSE: And now...
it's over!
- [gags]
- That should be
more than enough this time!
Miss Fortuna,
you need to be careful!
Keep your guard up!
I'll make sure that she's--
- Why, Geuse?
- [gasps]
Miss Emilia, what are you...
[sputters]
No, it can't be!
[gasping]
PANDORA: None of this
is your fault.
You were in a blind rage.
You mistook what you saw.
- [shuddering]
[wailing]
It can't be!
It can't be! It can't be!
- What did I just--
What did I just do?!
Impossible!
Why?! Why?! Why?! Why?!
Why?! Why did I do this?!
- That's simple.
It was all for love.
You offered up your very soul
for a chance to save
the one you cared about
more than anybody.
All that you've done
was the result of that emotion,
a beautiful,
wonderful symbol of love.
- Love. Love. Love...
- Yes. There's nothing
for you to fear
and nothing to regret.
This inevitable path
was the one you've chosen.
This is
what it was leading to,
and all the love that you're
feeling is not wrong.
- It's for love.
It's for love.
[crying]
- Emilia.
- [gasps] Yes, Mother?
- Dear brother.
I'm sorry I let you down.
- Don't say that.
- I couldn't do
any of the things...
you wanted and told me to do.
I know your wife...
will be so angry.
I've failed her.
She'll never forgive me.
- [gasps]
[crying]
[sniffles]
I'll forgive you. Is that okay?
You're my mother,
and I love you.
You've always taken care of me.
You loved me just as much
as my mom and dad did,
and I knew, no matter what,
you were by my side.
There's nothing you need
to say you're sorry for,
nothing at all.
Your Emilia
will always care for you...
so much!
So much, Mother Fortuna!
[crying] I love you.
I love you. I love you.
I love you.
- [sighs]
- [crying]
- Lia.
- [gasps]
Eh? Mother?
- My little crybaby.
- I love you...
so very much.
- Now, then, does this mean
you're ready to choose the hope
that you'll break the seal?
- What do you mean? I don't...
- The circumstances
have changed,
because the mother
you made your promise to
has sadly passed away.
Since you're no longer
shackled by any vows,
I assumed your decision
would be a bit easier.
What do you say?
[wind blowing]
- I say die.
PANDORA: What
a dangerous thing to do.
- Die.
- What brought that--
PANDORA: Please, calm yourself.
We can talk it over
until you under--
- I said die.
- Such viciousness
from a tenderhearted child.
Your mother
would be sad if you--
- Now die.
- This is quite a problem.
It's having the opposite effect.
Just die.
Die! Die! Die! Die!
Die! Die!
Die!
Die! Die...
- It's a shame when my wish
is just out of reach,
but it's time
to end this for today.
To continue
beyond your current state
might force you
into the impossible.
- Die! Die!
You need to die!
Just die! Die...
- At the rate you're going,
I'd say there's
a high likelihood
that you'll fall
into a deep sleep soon.
- Die! Die...
- The power you're
releasing
will envelop this forest
with frozen soil
that will never thaw.
Either your mana
will eventually run dry...
or it'll be offset
at some point.
But that could only happen
through someone
with power comparable to yours.
Until then...
- You need to die!
You need to die!
You need to die...
- Sorry, but I
won't be doing that.
- Die! Die...
- As surely
as the seasons change,
as surely as snow melts
and the glacial period ends,
we will meet again.
- Die! Die...
However, it would make me sad
if you still hated me
when that day arrives.
- You need to die!
You need to die!
You need to die...
- So to make sure
that doesn't happen,
your memories thus far
will end with today,
as you forget my existence.
- [gasps]
- Fill the empty void
that's left behind
however you wish.
And, indeed,
you did your very best
to keep your promise
to your mother.
I'd be pleased if you'd
engrave that in your heart
and remain torn between duty
and your own regret forever.
- [gasps]
[music playing]
- I look forward to the day when
our two paths cross once again.
[no audible dialogue]
[Geuse laughing]
[echoing laughter fades]
[wind howling]
- [gasping]
M-Mother.
[howling wind stops]
[music playing]
ECHIDNA: If you blame yourself
for falsifying your memories,
I'd say you're barking
up the wrong tree altogether.
The one you saw all those years
ago was the Witch of Vanity.
I'm certain it was her Authority
that padded out
your distorted recollections.
- Regarding Pandora,
could I ask you about her?
- I have been known to seek out
conversations with others,
but in your case, I have
no interest in digressions.
- I see. All right.
I'm responsible
for turning them all into ice,
and I did it when they were
struggling to try and rescue me.
- By recalling the past,
you saw the end of your anguish.
The only thing that remains
is to give your answer.
- To what?
Do you mean the trial?
- The first one
comes to a conclusion
whenever you find
the courage necessary
to part with
your greatest regret,
either by accepting
or rejecting
that which is your past self.
- [breathes deeply]
- The fact remains that the
repercussions of your own sin
caused your mother,
your friends, and your family
to turn into a collection
of ice statues.
Your determination to save them
can't even be called idealistic.
Ultimately, it was
no more than a dream.
So what could possibly
be left for you?
- Well, that's simple.
It's all so clear to me now.
Mother loved and protected me
as if I was her own,
which is why I wanted to do
everything within my power
to see that she was rescued.
I wanted to sleep
in her arms again
together in the same bed.
I wanted to tell her over
and over how much I loved her.
- Are you saying
you feel contrite?
- No, of course not.
Why would I?
I stood my ground,
refused to yield,
and kept my promise.
I don't regret it.
If I'm disappointed
about anything,
it's that I wasn't
strong enough at that age,
wasn't smart enough
to do better.
But I'll never regret
keeping the solemn vow
I made with Mother
and not giving in
to what Pandora wanted,
not for a single day.
Because...
[no audible dialogue]
Mother told me in the very end
she was proud of me
for keeping my promise to her.
She said that I was
her greatest treasure.
- But given that you
can't save her now,
doesn't that mean
you've completely lost
your reason to fight?
- No, I don't see it that way.
- While I couldn't
rescue Mother,
I can't say that for
certain
about everyone else
yet.
They're still
sleeping in the ice,
waiting for me
to finally set them free,
and I'm the only one
who's able to do it.
- The forest was contaminated
by the Black Serpent.
Even if you thaw
the frozen soil,
what if their bodies have
become corroded by disease?
What if none of the land
your people owned
for generations remains?
- You're just
imagining the worst.
They're all hoping
to be released.
I need to wake each of them up
soon and let them scold me.
Then they'll smile and tell me
they're so happy
I'm still alive.
- What a foolish delusion.
- Not at all.
It's the prediction
of a bright future.
Mother told me that, one day,
each of us
would leave the forest
and have the chance
to live out normal lives.
In exactly the same way
we were friends
with Geuse and his people
and the way Subaru confessed
that he was in love with me,
the world where Geuse and Mother
should have walked
side by side will come!
There's no doubt about it!
- Are the villagers
who turned into ice statues
in this imaginary world, too,
all the ones you froze
and have long since abandoned?
- Yes! Each one of them.
And I'll apologize
over and over
'til they choose to forgive me.
After my apologies
have been accepted,
I can show them all
a beautiful world,
then tell them we don't
need
to live in hiding anymore.
They'll see
that this is the world
Mother Fortuna told us about!
[inhales]
I'll sing my dreams
'til my throat goes dry!
That way, even Mother up
in the skies above will hear me!
I'll tell her that I'm
going to live happily
in the world she dearly loved
for the rest of my life!
[ice shatters]
- I understand.
Yes, it's clear to me now.
I thought I understood before,
but this exceeds
my expectations.
You really are that pushy,
insolent, brazen,
and delusional,
the peak of hypocrisy.
- Maybe.
Is that bad?
- Your trial's officially over.
Regardless of its
rather self-absorbed ending,
your past has
most definitely been settled.
Continue using your mother's
sacrifice as an excuse.
Then her martyrdom
will see your pompous wish
to the very end.
- Say what you want
to try and hurt me.
It's fine. I'm used
to your constant insults by now.
- [sighs]
One trial down,
and two more remain.
I must say
I'm sincerely looking forward
to more of your
pathetic struggling.
- Huh? Hold on.
I still have more trials
to go through?
There's two more.
So that's three in all?
- Don't worry.
I doubt the next ones
will pose that much
of a challenge for you.
- Oh, they won't?
- Now that you've
been fighting back,
they'll likely be
quite a poor fit.
In a sense, you've abandoned
all thought entirely.
- Oh, wow. That's really mean.
- [chuckles]
Well, I do despise you,
remember?
- That may be true,
but I don't hate you
half as much as you hate me.
[chorus vocalizing]
[groans]
[sighs]
Thanks. I appreciate it.
[whimpers]
Mother Fortuna...
I'm so sorry.
[crying]
Mother, I...
I'm so sorry!
[crying]
SUBARU:
Sorry to push you like that,
but you told me
a lot more than I expected.
Thank you.
- I've had this fear
for some time
that removing the barrier
would trample
upon the wishes of Ryuzu Meyer,
the ancestor to each one of us.
- I get how you feel,
but I have total confidence
in Emilia,
so when she aces the trial
with flying colors
and everything works out
the way that it should,
we'll be able to call
the whole world a Sanctuary.
- Then I will leave
these matters to you, Young Su.
- Just take it easy.
Your wish of 400 years
is on me now.
- Okay, then. I'd like
to let Shima rest for a while.
Hey, Ram, you think you
can take care of that for me?
- Ah! Old Hag Shi's hideout
would be better
than Old Hag Ryu's place
for a little downtime.
I can go with 'em and make su--
- Whoa, wait a minute,
Garfiel!
I don't think you should be
pushing yourself yet, either.
We need to let Miss Ram
and Miss Ryuzu handle this.
- Really?
- Listen, if a brute like you
charged at Miss Shima
and interrupted her rest,
then it would defeat
the purpose entirely.
- I suppose I should go,
too, as suggested.
- Thank you. I would
appreciate that very much.
I'd feel guilty
leaving Miss Ryuzu
in the care of two men
who clearly lack
any shred of empathy.
- That's right.
Hang on here!
You weren't counting me
as one of those two men,
were--
So then I guess Miss Ram
must have sensed
what's likely to happen?
Well, the fact
that she just overlooked--
[sighs] No, wait.
The fact she was willing
to help us at all
meant there was reason
to keep hoping.
- That's enough, you guys.
I can't take it anymore!
Don't just walk around
and talk in code,
ignorin' me like one guy
with ten morgrelo!
- We'd both be stuck
if you left us behind,
and since Ram
is an unknown variable,
I wanted her
out of the group.
- Wait. You what? Hang on.
I don't understand a damn thing
that you're sayin' anymo--
- Okay, listen.
We're on our way
to pay a visit
to Margrave Mathers now.
- Huh?
- And you have two arms,
plus both of us
dragging you down.
That should be enough
to get there, right?
- We just need to make it back
before Emilia comes out,
because there's no way
I wanna miss that.
- Well, look who we have here.
Never did I expect you
to stop by at a time like this.
What brings you
to my humble abode at this hour?
SUBARU: Look at you.
Greeting us in full makeup, huh?
It's embarrassing when you're
that eager to see us.
- You may make such commentary
and pointed judgments
if you wish,
but let me remind you
that you're the one
who said the next time we met,
I should be made up again.
- Yeah, you're right.
I guess I did say that.
- But in any event,
my grand attire,
along with these cosmetics,
are my way of preparing
for a fight I can't lose.
- I see. So it's literally
your uniform and war paint.
- Enough about me, Subaru.
Let's get back
to what brings you here.
- Well, I think
you should know by now
that the game board
you set up so carefully
is completely falling apart.
- Yes, indeed I do.
And seeing
who you've brought with you
tells me that the situation
has changed.
I must say
they've certainly succeeded
in taming you,
haven't they, Garfiel?
- What?!
- Easy, boy.
The one who concerns me the most
among you is actually...
- You mean--Is it me?
- From the moment you came
into this room, I wondered,
"Just who could
this cloaked lad be, anyway?"
- Damn, Otto! Imagine that!
You actually got left out
of the prophecy
foretelling the future!
- That doesn't make me
feel good at all,
and it's pretty hard to hide
how shocked I am
that none of this makes sense!
- Clearly somebody like this
is here as a witness
to the battle
between Subaru and me.
Interesting. His mere presence
must mean that I--
- Now you're getting it.
The first gear's
come out of alignment.
- OTTO: Huh?
- Everything you've been
setting up so very carefully
has been disrupted
by an unknown factor.
That's starting
to change the flow.
All thanks
to my insignificant friend here,
who isn't even mentioned
anywhere in the prophecy.
["Believe In You" playing]
- Apologies, but would you
mind
telling me your name again?
- [sighs]
[gasps]
[sighs]
My name is Otto Suwen,
And I feel honored
to have this rare opportunity
to make your acquaintance,
truly.
Even though I'm nothing more
than a humble merchant,
it's my great pleasure.
- I shall remember that then,
Otto Suwen.
The next time we meet,
you will not be overlooked.
This, I can assure you.
- Way to go! Good for you, Otto!
You left a bigger impression
on Roswaal than ever,
like you hoped for!
- This wasn't how I wanted him
to remember me, though!
This whole situation
is just weird!
- So thanks to him,
you managed to make it
back on your feet
thus finding the spirit
and backbone needed
for the last fight.
- That about covers it.
But yeah, you're right, Otto.
It does seem kinda weird.
Shouldn't it be the main heroine
getting me back on my feet
instead of someone like you
playing that role?
Thanks a lot for stepping
in
and messing everything
up.
- Why are you acting like
all of this is my fault?
- I don't know why, either!
- Come on.
I'm just kidding, man. [laughs]
- I will ask you once more.
Why is it you've
come here to see me?
- [gasps]
To say you need to surrender.
- [grunts]
- Thanks to Shima,
I know the truth now,
the real reason
behind the Sanctuary,
and it's time for us
to talk about it.