[ice shatters]
[Puck crying]
I'm sorry...
s-so sorry.
[crying]
EMILIA: Tell me,
why are you crying?
- Because I just
left you all alone.
- I don't understand.
What do you mean?
- Because I--
I couldn't--
I couldn't find you
all this time.
- Easy. I'm right here, okay?
- [continues crying]
- By the way, what's your name?
- Oh, yeah.
I guess you don't know it,
do you?
[music playing]
[birds chirping]
[footsteps crunching]
EMILIA: I know this is
just a dream world,
but I can smell the air.
I can even feel the dirt.
That's so strange, isn't it?
Are you listening?
Hey, Echidna?
[leaves rustling]
[gasps]
I'm sorry!
Are you all right?
Was I walking
a little too quickly?
- Oh, save your fake sympathy.
You don't think those words
will change my attitude, do you?
If so,
then you're quite foolish.
- [sighs] I was
genuinely worried about you.
- I need none of your concern
whatsoever.
There were a few too many dreams
happening at once. That's all.
It will adjust itself soon
slowly, but surely. See?
- [gasps]
- Consider the name "dreamworld"
to be merely
a figurative expression.
More accurately,
it's a separate world
replicating the memories
and reflecting the consciousness
of those who choose
to undergo the trial.
- Thanks for that.
I appreciate the explanation,
even though you don't like me.
- Hmph. Just don't get
any ridiculous ideas
about me actually being
a nice person or anything.
It's simply my nature
to answer any questions
that are asked of me.
I understand.
- Do you remember the pathetic
struggle you endured
the last time
you attempted the trial?
- I was so helpless then.
I can't even argue
with your description of it.
I guess
I covered up my memories
because I didn't want
to see them.
Maybe that's why I can't even
recall one of them on my own.
Everything's just so fuzzy.
Even now,
I'm still not prepared.
- Then it would be no surprise
if you failed again, right?
Making an excuse before you
even start is awfully defeatist.
- No, it's not that.
I've thought of a way to use
this place to ready myself.
[birds chirping]
ECHIDNA: I'm assuming
this is no ordinary tree.
There was something
you desperately wanted
to keep locked up inside it.
- This is the Princess Room.
I was often sent here to play
back when I was little.
Oh, right.
I can't touch the door.
Could we just walk
through it instead?
Huh?
[music playing]
[gasps]
- The young one
is clearly you, isn't it?
Even though you weren't
aware of anything yet,
you look
so annoyingly carefree.
- Are you going to complain
about me at every age?
Besides, now I--
[sighs]
It's my Mother Fortuna.
- Emilia, I need to go
and take care of something,
so you stay here in this room,
and be good, all right?
- Is it
something important again?
- [laughs]
That silver hair of yours
is exactly like my brother's.
However, I believe
your gentle features
come from your mother's side,
'cause everyone
from my side has mean eyes
Oh, no! They're two of the
prettiest ones I've ever seen!
- That woman's Mother Fortuna,
my father's younger sister.
My real parents
were always too busy
with their responsibilities
to make time for me,
which meant that most of my days
were spent in her care.
[door creaks]
[bolt clanks]
- [moans]
I'm so bored!
Why does she
hide everything from me?
Mother says lying
and secrets are wrong!
Right?!
I wish I could go outside.
Huh?
Uh, hi.
[gasps]
Hey! Hold on! No fair!
- [breeze blowing]
- Huh?
[gasps]
[birds chirping]
[grunting]
Ah.
Mother Fortuna and everyone else
keeps secrets from me,
so this should make us even!
[grunts]
[village chatter]
Sneaky, sneak.
[gasps]
[yelps]
[grunts]
[music playing]
FORTUNA: I want to thank you.
You've done so much for us
time and time again.
- That isn't necessary.
I know we've brought you
more than your share
of inconveniences.
- Well, the same could also
be said for us, Geuse.
- Also...
I know that I ask this
every time we meet,
but does the seal remain intact?
- Yes, don't worry.
There have been no changes.
And it needs to stay that way.
If the worst were to happen,
I could never face
my brother and sister.
- Your brother and his wife,
you mean?
- It's all right.
I'm aware of that.
But no matter the circumstances,
I mustn't forget
the responsibility
I've been tasked to carry.
I don't want to abandon it
or see it partway.
Don't you feel the same?
- Well, actually...
[sighs] to be completely
honest with you,
I don't have anything else.
So I suppose it's a different
sense of responsibility
from yours.
Obsession, regret...
I'm clinging to things that
might as well be delusions.
- [sighs]
Thanks to the spirits,
the seasons don't change
very much in the forest,
but you continue to bring us
things like clothing and
books.
We truly appreciate it.
Thank you, as always.
- [sighs]
Truthfully, I don't agree
with forcing all of you
to live in such
an inconvenient place like this.
It won't ever seem right to me.
- Come on. Don't just call it
"a place like this."
Think you're forgetting that
everybody here loves the
forest.
- Miss Fortuna!
- Eh?
- All the items
have been transferred.
- Thank you, Archi.
I appreciate it.
- I can see you're only growing
more and more dependable,
aren't you?
- As part of the next generation
of forest dwellers,
I know I can't be regarded
as a novice forever.
- I pray that your good health
will persevere,
for the forest and the seal,
for your family, and of course
for yourself as well.
Oh, yes,
I almost forgot to ask you.
About Miss Emilia,
does she remain in good health?
- [gasps]
- No need to worry.
She's growing into
a very kindhearted
and healthy young lady.
But I apologize.
I still can't allow her
to meet you.
- It's all right.
As long as I know
Miss Emilia's growing up safe
and in good health,
then that'll be enough.
A sinner such as myself
wouldn't ever dare to ask
for anything more than
that.
- Bishop Romanée-Conti...
- [gasps]
- are you ready?
- Yes. I'm all finished here.
It's time for us transgressors
to be on our way.
Miss Fortuna,
until next time then.
- Even if no one else here
will say it,
please know that we're
extremely grateful to you,
and I truly mean that.
- That's kind of you to say.
Your words of praise alone
would surely carry me through
a hundred years of turmoil.
[wind blowing]
- [sighs]
- Miss Fortuna,
are you feeling tired or--
- Of course not! Don't treat me
like such an old lady.
I know I may seem elderly
compared to
a young boy like you,
but I'm still in good shape.
- Th--No, that wasn't
what I meant at all!
I just thought
this must be hard
when you also have
the forest dweller duties.
- Then maybe I'll take advantage
of your kindness
and let you handle
the rest of them.
Right now I need to go
and free a little princess
who must be getting
pretty bored.
- [gasps]
What do I do? What do I do?
What do I do?
What do--[yelps]
What do I do? What do--
What do I do? What do I do?
[gasps] Oh, no.
[gasps]
[energy surges]
Wow.
- Emilia, are you awake?
- Uh, y-yes, I'm awake!
But...[sighs]
- But what?
- Why are you so flustered?
- [glass clatters]
[gasps]
- Um, I-I'm sorry.
I wanted to draw, but I
spilled the ink everywhere.
- Ah, dear.
Mother Fortuna, I-I'm sorry.
Honestly, you worry
about things too much.
You don't need to be so afraid.
I'm not angry, okay?
You didn't hurt yourself,
did you?
[cloth flutters]
- What's wrong?
- Nothing. It's nothing.
I just really missed you today.
That's all.
- Uh...
- You spoiled girl.
Hey. Wanna know something?
- Hmm?
- I love you.
ECHIDNA: Perhaps the sights you
locked deep within your heart
have begun to overlap,
intertwining with scenes
from your memories a bit.
- I'm shocked.
I thought you'd have
some stinging comments ready,
mean and petty things
to say about Mother and me.
- Even if that's
what you thought I would do,
I wouldn't recommend
putting that out in the open
and saying so.
My opinion of you
is already low enough.
And with these
petty accusations,
you're making it
plummet even further.
- Oh, no need to worry.
I hadn't planned
on telling anyone about this
to begin with.
- For better or for worse,
it seems the influence
that boy's had over you
has grown rather strong.
- You think so?
Thanks for telling me.
- [sighs]
Anyway,
back to the task at hand.
You've recalled your mother,
some people you knew,
and that so-called fairy.
Are you ready
to face your past now?
- No, not yet.
- [gasps]
- There are still some
important memories I'm missing.
- What more could there be?
- There's the seal.
- Little fairy, let's get going.
We're escaping again today.
[gasps]
- Hello? Emilia?
- [yelps]
- Hmm? Is something the matter?
- Nope! I'm just fine.
What was it you needed, Archi?
- Well, first thing's first.
I thought I'd bring
some snacks over for you.
Now eat these up,
and be a good girl, all right?
- Okay. Thanks.
Archi's been
such a worrywart lately,
so I need to be extra careful.
[yelps]
[grunts]
Geuse's group
is here again today.
I thought
whatever they were hiding
would be something fun.
Mother and the others
are really weird.
FORTUNA: I have to say
Emilia's been
so full of energy lately.
She's always coming home
with her clothes all muddy.
- [laughs] That she's so lively
can only be a good thing.
I'll bring some new clothes
for her soon.
- You've already done so much.
I'm sorry to be asking
for even more.
But do you have
adult clothes, too?
- Yes, of course we do.
So why not take a look?
I'm sure we have
something
that would be lovely on
you.
- [gasps] Hold on.
We may have known
each other a long time,
but there's no need
to embarrass me
- with comments like that!
- [grunts]
I only spoke
what I felt to be the truth.
Was there something strange
about how I said it?
- [sighs]
- Uh...
eh?
- [gasps]
Hey, uh, what are you doing?
- Oh, I-I was just
remembering something.
There was once a time
when you seemed unhappy
while talking to me,
and it turned out
you had a rather high fever.
You're not warm now, though.
- Come on.
You're just being silly.
That was decades ago.
Stop treating me like a child!
You're so ridiculous.
- [groans]
That stupid Geuse!
Oh, yeah!
And stupid Archi, too!
- [sneezes]
[groans]
GEUSE: Tell me,
does the seal
still remain in place?
- Just as always, yes.
It's very conscientious of you
to check on it
each time you're here.
- That is my duty after all.
The state of affairs
outside the forest
is dubious at the moment.
Perhaps my concern is baseless,
but I wanted you to be aware.
- Of course.
- Please continue
being diligent
for Miss Emilia
and for the two of them as well.
- Wait. What seal?
Huh?
[chuckles]
Yes, please. [giggles]
[footsteps crunching]
[music playing]
ECHIDNA: A door?
Strange to see one out here.
EMILIA: This is the seal.
And its very existence
is the reason.
- So you found the answer,
did you?
- This is what they've
been talking about?
- Some other guy saw my letter
to the girl who I'm
in love with before she did.
[whimpers]
My life is over.
- Aw, come on. You're way
too damn depressed about this.
Gotta try and get ahold
of yourself, man.
- I never imagined
that Garfiel would be there
in the shadows
waiting to settle the score.
- Look, you're always
hitting on her
in front of other people,
anyway.
So why get
so embarrassed about it
just because you put it
in writing this time?
- Normally I'm prepared for
her
to brush off stuff like this.
Since that's
what always happens,
I've gotten used to it!
But I was going for broke
and being serious for once!
And it was literally
a late-night love letter,
the most embarrassing kind!
- Hey, don't beat yourself up
about it, boss.
If anything, it made me wish
that I could sponge off
of your good luck.
"In matters of love,
follow the lingdorn's example."
Am I right?
- I know you wanna
make me feel better,
but no matter what you say,
it still sounds
like you're just trying
to pick a fight with me!
[Subaru groans] It took Garfiel
about an hour for the trial
when he went in,
so I guess
it'll take her about the same.
- If she successfully
completes it, that is.
[groans]
RAM: Try to take a hint
for a change.
- Huh? Ow!
- You're this oblivious, and
you call yourself a merchant?
- Comments like that
hurt a lot more
- than a flick to the forehead.
- Anyway...
Miss Shima would like to have
a word with you, Barusu.
She wants to continue
the discussion from last night.
- What did Gran--Uh, I mean,
what did the old hag
wanna talk to you about
for so long, boss?
- There's no point in trying
to cover it up now,
because we all know
you're a granny's boy.
Mostly, she told me
what happened
when you went
into the graveyard.
- Oh, really?
- I had my hands full yesterday
figuring out
how to deal with Garfiel.
And even though
most things were sorted out,
we still put off
the most important part.
RAM: What are you
referring to, exactly?
SUBARU: Well...
SHIMA: It is a subject
that is quite unavoidable
if you truly wish
to liberate the Sanctuary.
[wind blowing]
- [grunting]
This door's strange.
Why won't it fall over?
I don't understand how it works.
But thanks to all of you,
I at least managed to find it!
Yay, everyone!
Now what?
This whole thing
is Mother Fortuna's fault,
and it's Geuse's fault, too.
Nyah!
Okay, time to go home.
Today I think
I'll paint the sky red
and then use white
for the whole forest!
[panting]
Eh?
Hey, what's wrong?
Is something gonna happen?
[chuckles]
[brush rustles]
GEUSE: This is quite a problem.
- [gasps]
- I might not make it
by the appointed time.
Eh?
Oh.
And what cute little child
might this be?
- [whimpers]
Please, sir, I beg you
to let me on my way
and show mercy.
- Well, well, My goodness.
What an adorable young lady.
[gasps]
- Huh?
- Wait.
Don't tell me that you're--
No. You can't be her.
[gasps]
- What's wrong?
You okay, Geuse?
- [crying]
Yes. I'm fine.
Of course.
Yes, I couldn't be better.
Nothing is wrong
in the slightest.
Do you want to know why?
Because I--[cries]
Because I've just...
been granted salvation
like never before!
- Eh, really?
If you've been saved,
then why are you crying?
- It's quite simple.
I'm not crying because I'm sad.
I'm so happy,
and I feel elated.
I'm truly blessed.
All of this joy can sometimes
bring warm tears to one's
eyes.
[crying]
You cry even when you're happy?
It's all right, Geuse. Easy.
It's all right.
- I know there are
so many things like this
that I'd forgotten.
It's still hard.
Not too long ago,
I wouldn't have been able
to accept this.
But now it's different.
I may be scared,
but I won't shy away in fear.
- You're opting to abandon
depending on a man
or father figure,
even though it's so typical
of a filthy woman like you?
- I'm sure
Subaru would forgive me
if I were to make that choice,
but I'd still be weak,
and that's something
I don't want to just shrug off.
Besides, I don't want
all those encouraging things
he wrote for me
to end up being wrong.
He really believes in me,
and that's why
I can't allow myself
to be embarrassed
by his feelings.
- Do what you believe
to be right.
Regardless of your path,
I will simply find satisfaction
in your suffering.
- So everything is ready now?
- That's correct,
and the warm-up round is over.
The trial that broke you once
is beginning for real.
Get ready.
GEUSE: Please wait, Miss Emilia!
It's dangerous
to run around like that!
- That's a big no!
Come on! Just try to catch me!
- [panting]
- She's pretty mischievous,
isn't she?
At times, even we
can barely handle her.
- It's good to be young
and full of such energy.
But I-I just wish
she would avoid
doing anything too dangerous.
If she could jump around
in her home,
healthy and bathed in sunlight,
with no concerns
about hurting herself
or breaking things--
- Geuse.
- Huh?
- Come on.
That wouldn't exactly be easy.
- [stammers]
You--You don't think so?
Well, for Miss Emilia's sake,
I only wish
there was some way to--
Some way to just--
- [laughs]
- EMILIA: Hey!
- [gasps]
- What's gotten
into you, anyway?
Why aren't either one
of you chasing me?
Aren't we still in the middle
of playing a game?
- Ah, I'm so sorry. Forgive me!
Never before have I made
such a terrible mistake!
Now, there's no need
to spoil her like that.
Emilia, come over here, please.
- Okay, Mother. Be right there.
[sighs]
Honestly, you are so spoiled.
Eep!
- Right into my trap.
It looks like
you've been captured,
which means I've
officially won the game.
- Aw, come on. No fair!
That's cheating!
You're playing dirty!
Say you're sorry!
- My goodness!
You're definitely a handful,
little girl.
Now let me ask you something.
Have you put
the least bit of thought
into what I said to you earlier?
Tell me,
why exactly do you think
Geuse and I were chasing you?
- Uh...
I-I can explain.
The fairies said
we should go outside and play,
so, I, uh...
- Seriously, Emilia,
you shouldn't blame things
on other people,
fairies or otherwise.
- [moans]
You're right. I'm sorry.
Since I made friends
with Geuse while I was out,
I only wanted to find a way
to tell you about it.
And since he's a crybaby,
I felt like I had to do
my part to help him.
- Now, that feeling is
something very special.
However, you made
a solemn oath to me
that you'd never go
to that place, didn't you?
- Eh, yes, I did.
- Well, then, you needed
to keep your word.
- [moans]
- Listen carefully.
A promise
is the embodiment of trust,
and to break it
is to betray that trust,
so you mustn't ever do it again.
You have to promise me, Emilia.
I want you to swear
that you'll do your best
to keep your vows
from this moment on.
- All right. I will.
[crying]
I'm really,
really sorry, Mother.
- Okay.
That's good enough for me.
- [crying]
[Geuse crying]
- And what about you, Geuse?
Are you all right?
- I-I'm sorry.
I-It was just
such a dazzling sight.
I couldn't--
I couldn't hold back my tears.
- [laughs]
- Uh...
- Anyway, Emilia.
- Eh?
- You mentioned
that fairies talked to you?
- Oh. Uh, yes, they do,
and they've been coming to
help me out for a long time now.
- Wanna see?
- Huh?
[gasps] Are these
lesser spirits?
I can't believe
how many there are!
- A wonderful surprise, indeed.
Miss Emilia possesses
the natural talent
to be a spirit user.
- Lesser spirits?
And what do you mean
by "spirit user"?
- The things
you've been calling fairies
are actually beings
known as lesser spirits.
Those who communicate with them,
form contracts with them,
and borrow their powers
are known as spirit users.
- You mean
I can be one of them?
- Hold on.
Please don't give her
any crazy ideas.
- I must point out
that Miss Emilia
won't be a little girl forever.
Knowing that,
at times in the future
when nobody's by her side,
they'll be a great source
of strength for her.
- Maybe, but that sounds
like it could be dangerous.
I can't let my sweet Emilia--
- Eh?
- Listen!
I'm on Geuse's side today!
He says I'm gonna be
a spirit user. So there!
- Nyah!
- You see?
She's taken you seriously.
So what are you going to do now?
- Oh, uh, well, I--
uh, I don't know.
I, uh...
What a predicament.
- Hmm?
You know, the way
that you two are carrying on,
you're acting like
a mommy and daddy.
- Wha--
D-Don't say
silly things like that!
Geuse and I have known
each other for a long time,
- that's all!
- Yes, that's right,
- Miss Emilia!
- That's why we speak--
- To one who's lived
as long as I have,
even Miss Fortuna
is little more than a child.
- [groans] Now I think that
may be going a bit too far.
I'll admit you are older,
but do you even know my age?
- No! Wait! I didn't mean to--
Just poor phrasing! I'm sorry!
Of course I'm quite aware
of your precise age,
and you are
certainly far too beautiful
and too mature
to be a mere child.
- Mm-hmm.
Very well, then.
I'll forgive you.
- [gasps]
- But look,
you'd better be really sorry.
- Uh, of course.
What I was trying to say,
though poorly,
is that I've known Miss Fortuna
for a long, long time,
more years
than you could imagine.
In fact, I've known her
since the days
when your mother and father--
- [gasps] Geuse!
- [gasps]
Oh! Forgive me.
- But what about
my mother and father?
["Believe in you" playing]
- I'm sorry, Emilia.
- Huh?
- We'll talk about that
another time.
Go on back to your room now.
- Hope you don't forget.
I'm gonna hold you
to that, okay? [groans]
[exhales]
- Come on. Be a good girl.
I know you can do that.
And if you're extra, extra good,
I'll let you see Geuse again
soon, too, all right?
- You really mean it?
You'll make a solemn vow,
and you won't break it?
- [chuckles]
- [gasps]
- Yes. You have my word.
It'll be a very important
promise, okay,
an oath sworn between us both.
- [grunts]
That's good enough for me.
Thank you.
I'll go back to my room now.
- Uh...
- I'll see you soon, Geuse.
Just be sure not to cry
too much, all right?
Make it a promise
until we both meet again.
- As you wish.
Because I'm certain
we'll meet again soon as well.
[singing in Japanese]
- There's someone
approaching now.
- Oh? [gasps]
[song ends]
- [both gasp]
- GEUSE: Huh?
[ominous music playing]
- Huh?
- Who are you?
- I do believe when you
want to know someone's name,
it's considered common courtesy
to give your own first,
is it not?
We've never seen one another
before, now, have we?
Therefore, I feel
we should be on equal footing
as far as building
a relationship goes.
What gives you the right to
demand my name ahead of yours?
You think you're
so much better than I am?
- I think I've heard enough.
For a man, you sure like
talking a lot, don't you?
- Oh, "for a man," you say?
Thanks for showing me
you don't even know any men
you could possibly
compare me to.
My, what an attitude.
I can't just
let that slide, you know.
Doing so would mean
disrespecting my individuality,
my authority, and my--
- I said enough!
Stop talking like you're
in love with yourself,
and tell me who you are!
[dramatic music playing]
- [chuckles]
I'm the Sin Archbishop
of the Witch's Cult,
representing Greed,
Regulus Corneas.