- Let me make it clear that
you're welcome to stay here.
I would gladly host
the both of you
for as long as you like,
whenever you like.
- We really appreciate that,
but for now,
it's important for us
to get the villagers back home.
- Once they've all settled in
and we talk
to Emilia's sponsor, Roswaal,
then we'll come back and
take you up on that offer.
- All right, very well.
When you do, I hope you'll
give me the opportunity
to repay my great debt to you.
- It's really
not that big of a deal.
'cause you helped us out,
too, you know.
And besides,
we already got a reward.
[chuckles] Right, Patrasche?
- [coos]
- [yelps]
- Are you all right, Subaru?
- Man, those scales
are rougher than I expected!
Now I know
how a piece of cheese feels
when it's being grated.
[both laugh]
- Okay...
I've got Rem tucked in
and secure for the trip!
Just keep her still, all right?
- Uh, sure.
- And let me remind you
that you'll need your rest
when you get back
to the mansion, too.
- You mean me?
- Ever since you went
head-to-head against Sloth,
that gate of yours
has been working overtime.
I did clean up
all the toxins in your gate,
but you need to let it rest
for at least a couple of months.
- Two months downtime.
Well, surely
all this crazy stuff
can't keep happening
for that long.
Wait! I didn't
just jinx myself, did I?!
- Okay, I guess it's about time
for you to get going now.
Oh, yeah! Miss Crusch,
think you wanted to give 'em
a few parting words, didn't
you?
- Well, Miss Emilia, I want
to wish you a safe journey.
Stay in good health,
and I look forward
to seeing you again soon.
- [sighs]
You, too, Miss Crusch.
Take good care of yourself.
And next time, I won't be
the one who constantly
needs saving.
I'll be someone who can
step up and help others.
- [chuckles]
Mr. Subaru Natsuki,
I wish you a safe journey
and all the best
in the future as well.
- Uh...
[sighs]
- [trills]
- Until we meet again,
take care of yourselves
[wagons rattling]
- Guess we're on our way.
- [gasps]
You know, Subaru,
you always seem to sit beside me
as if it's the obvious choice.
- Oh, is there
something wrong with that?
- Mm-mmm. It did seem
a little odd at first,
but I must admit
it feels strange
if you don't now, so it's fine.
- [gasps] All of
my painstaking efforts
have finally been rewarded!
This is just the best!
- Now you're
just teasing me again.
I know you're
still worried about Rem.
There's no need for you
to hide that from me.
- Uh...
- She's important to you,
isn't she?
- She is! You have no idea!
She's just as important
to me as you are!
- I'm not sure if you're
aware of this, but...
you're being very selfish.
- You're right.
Frankly, I feel so scummy,
I wish I could die,
but even so,
it's the absolute truth.
- Subaru, I...
- Hey, did you just say my name?
- Uh...
- Huh?
- I know I didn't.
Hold on. Have you
been there all this time?
- Do you think this thing
just drives itself?
Of course I've been here!
Why do you think
I decided to work with you
in the first place?!
- I'm only kidding! You're here,
because you want to negotiate
with Roswaal in person.
I haven't forgotten that.
- Come on. Stop joking around.
I'm begging you!
My whole life
is riding on this, okay?!
- Yeah, yeah, I got it.
I got it.
We're gonna say goodbye
to you for now,
- though, all right?
- What? Hey, wai--
[both laugh]
- I'm certain
you'll get her back
and you'll find some way
to help her.
- [gasps]
You really think so?
- I also believe that you and I
have something
of a selfish trait in common.
We both base each of our actions
on our own desires.
I realize I'm participating
in the royal selection
for selfish reasons, too.
- What do you mean by that?
- I'm sorry. Guess I'm not doing
a very good job
of explaining it.
It's not like I want
to hide anything from you,
but I'm just not sure
how to put it into words.
- Uh...
[sighs]
Don't worry about it.
We can talk everything out
after we join up with Roswaal.
- [gasps] Huh?
- And besides,
he might even know something
about what happened to Rem!
- [grunts]
OTTO: Okay, you two!
We'll be reaching
our destination in no time!
[overlapping chatter]
[Petra sighs]
So where is everybody?
- [panting]
This whole place is deserted.
- What?
- [gasping]
- Ram and the others haven't
returned from the Sanctuary?
- Doesn't look like it, huh?
By the way, Mili,
do you know happen to know
where the Sanctuary is?
- Huh? Hold on.
I thought you knew where it was.
- Huh?
- [both stammer]
- I know it might seem
a little late to be asking this,
but what kind of place are
we talking about, anyway?
- Actually, I'm not sure.
Roswaal just said it was sort
of
like a secret base and that...
- That what?
- Uh...
oh, it's nothing.
Really sorry. I guess I should
have asked for more details.
- No, no! Even if we
were
in a hurry to get to
safety,
I'm the one who was being
way too careless here!
- Uh...
- [all groan]
- We'll just have to head
to the mansion for right now.
Maybe we can even find
some clues there.
Hey, Otto!
You should come with us!
- What?! Over to the mansion?
SUBARU: We've come this far.
Don't be scared.
Take the carriage
and ground dragons
around back, okay?
OTTO: A-All right.
SUBARU: We're here, Rem.
We're back.
- Are you okay?
- Yeah.
Come to think of it,
I don't remember
locking the door when we left.
Think we got robbed?
- Beatrice stayed here,
so there's really
no need to worry.
Maybe she'll even answer
the door for us if we
knock.
- [chuckles] She might come
flying right through it,
looking for Puck.
- You could be right.
How are you, Puck?
You awake?
Huh. I guess not.
He's not responding.
- Hope someone here does.
[woman] Yes? One moment, please.
- Huh?
- Welcome home, Miss Emilia.
I've been anxiously awaiting
your inevitable return.
- Wait. Frederica?
- [chuckles]
Yes, it is I, Frederica, ready--
- Look at those chompers!
- Allow me to introduce myself.
My name is Frederica Baumann.
I worked here previously
and have returned.
- Uh, now that you mention it,
I was told
there was another maid who quit
just before I came here.
- Yes, I merely took
a temporary leave of absence
for some personal reasons.
At Ram's request,
I ended my respite
and returned to my post,
only to find the mansion empty.
Fortunately, a letter I found
in the master's office
gave me a good idea
as to what happened.
- A letter?
- So what made Ram
ask you to come back?
- Upon my return to this place,
I found the kitchen
and the trees in the garden
in quite a desolate state.
It was rather awful.
- That's a pretty
serious reason!
- Hmph!
- It is sort of strange, though.
Ram always worked
exceptionally hard for us
during the time
that you were away,
so why,
in just the past few days--
[gasps]
SUBARU: With Rem gone,
Ram couldn't handle
the mansion alone,
so she asked Frederica
to help? Huh.
- Would you mind explaining
who this girl
who looks so much like Ram is?
The resemblance is striking.
- That's her younger sister,
named Rem,
and she's a really nice girl.
She's so strong and kind
and a super-hard worker.
Even a stranger could tell
that she and Ram
were extremely close.
And I'm sure you were
a good friend to her, too.
- [sighs]
- Though you probably
don't remember at all, huh?
- Unfortunately, no.
I wonder how the master
and Ram will react
when they return
and discover our guest.
- There's no telling
what Roswaal will do.
I don't even want to try
to imagine how Ram will react.
- Oh, that reminds me.
Have you heard anything
from Roswaal, by the way?
Sadly, in these situations,
I have no way
of truly knowing what goes on
in the master's mind.
To the best of my knowledge,
there are only two people
in this world
he trusts enough to
share
those intimate details
with.
- And they are?
- Ram and the great spirit
of this mansion's
forbidden library.
- Great spirit
of the forbidden library?
- I'm referring to Beatrice.
- Hmm?
[grunts]
Hey, Beako! Long time no see!
- Oh, it's you.
No wonder the mansion
suddenly seemed so noisy.
SUBARU: Everyone's been worried
about you, you know.
Even if it's not right now,
you should apologize.
- Is that so? Why, exactly?
I fail to comprehend
why I must apologize
and to whom, I suppose.
- Well, if you'd prefer,
I could always do it for you.
I'll tell them
you were thanking me
with tears and snot
streaming down your face.
- Don't make up
such ridiculous stories!
I haven't shed tears
in a very long time, I suppose.
- I mean, It never hurts
to have a good wail
every once in a while.
- Those words carry
an extra level
of deep meaning
coming from you,
a man who bawled in the lap
of the woman he loves.
- Oh, would you
please just forget
about that incident, already?
- Could you please get
to the point, I suppose?
Pathetic weakling.
- Oh, yeah. [sighs]
I'm curious.
Exactly how well do you
know
what Roswaal is thinking?
- Hmm?
- See, I heard from somebody
that you can read him
pretty well.
- So is it true or not?
- Who said--
Aha. It must have been
that half-beast girl
who just came back to work.
I admit there may be
a bit of accuracy
to what she told you, I suppose.
However, my connection
with Roswaal has nothing to do
with the current circumstances,
understand?
- But you stayed here
at the mansion
all by yourself, right?
And without a single
countermeasure in place.
- I'm more than capable
of protecting myself,
thank you, which is the reason
I stayed, I suppose,
and Roswaal doesn't have
anything to do with that.
Although, guess I
couldn't honestly say
that he had nothing
on his mind at all, I suppose.
- Huh.
So were you and I
and everybody else
just giving him
the benefit of the doubt
about this
Witch's Cult situation,
thinking that he wouldn't
go up against them
without some kind of plan?
Oh, that's right.
- Look at this.
- Huh? [gasps]
A Gospel.
Now why do you, of all people,
possess one of those?!
- Just consider it
the spoils of battle.
It used to belong
to the guy in charge
of the witch cultists
who surrounded the mansion.
- I see. What became of him?
- He's dead now.
I was the one who killed him.
- Then it seems that you've
left me behind, too, I
suppose,
Betelgeuse.
- Eh, wait.
What'd you say?
- [sighs] None of your concern.
All right,
back to the matter at hand.
If you managed to destroy Sloth,
a Sin Archbishop,
then what happened
to his Witch Factor, I suppose?
- His what? Witch Factor?
- You seriously have
no idea what it is?
Well, if that's the case,
then why'd you even bother
to kill Sloth
in the first place?
And what exactly
is Roswaal doing--
- We went over this already,
remember?
Roswaal is at the Sanctuary,
and I'm the one
who wants to figure out
what he's thinking!
- The answers you seek
lie in the Sanctuary.
You'll find what you
want to know, I suppose
- [gasps] Seriously?
- His true intentions,
the meaning of the Gospel,
answers about the Witch Factor,
everything, they're all there.
If you want them,
then that's the place.
The half-beast girl
you met earlier
can lead you down there,
I suppose.
- Now hang on a second!
What's up with you?
Why are you so willing
to talk to me all of a sudden?
Also, why do I have to go
to the Sanctuary when you--
- I am not telling you.
I have the right to refuse
acknowledging your questions.
- [gasps]
- You've been told
how to find your answers.
Don't expect me to indulge you
any further, I suppose!
- Beako! Beatrice, please!
- Now begone.
I'm not a tool to be used
for your convenience!
- [yells]
- [humming a tune]
[both yell]
- [groans] Wh-What in the world
are you doing?!
Why did you fly into me just
as I was leaving the
bathroom?!
- Why did you have that look
on your face?
It seemed like you were
just about to cry again.
- Uh, do you think you
could get off of me now?
- So you really are allowed
to enter Miss Beatrice's
forbidden library.
- What do you mean by that?
You thought I wouldn't be?
- Well, Miss Emilia told me
what a reliable and
dependable person you are,
and she was quite thorough
in explaining
- exactly why she felt this way.
- Huh?
- So I must admit I was hoping
you'd live up to the hype.
- Huh?
- Hey, Frederica!
- Hold on!
What was it that you told her?!
- Wait. Listen!
It's not like that!
I did tell her about you,
yes, but she's
exaggerating.
- Oh, yeah? I happened to hear
what you said also.
It made me think there must be
more to Mr. Natsuki
than meets the eye.
- Not you, too, Otto!
- Aw, man! This sucks!
Why wasn't I around to hear
what you said about me?!
- I could never say it
in front of you, anyway.
All right, Frederica,
back
to what you were telling
us.
- [chuckles]
I do apologize, Miss. Of course.
I believe we need
to talk this over
so you don't find yourself
at a dead end.
- Uh, what do you
mean by that?
- Even if you were able
to see Beatrice,
whether she'd answer
your question or not
is quite another matter.
After all, the one thing
that both of you have in common
is your stubbornness.
- That description
is way too cute,
but yeah, you're right.
And what else?
- Well, there's a lot I want
to talk to Roswaal about also,
which is why I asked
Frederica to help us
by telling me
where the Sanctuary is.
- The half-beast girl
you met earlier
can lead you down there,
I suppose.
- So you're gonna tell
us
where to find it,
Frederica?
- Well, I was no match
for Miss Emilia's persistence,
even though I have been told
not to disclose
any more than is necessary.
But I'd like to ask
for a little time
to prepare for everything.
I think two days should do it.
- To prepare, huh?
Oh, yeah, that's right.
We'd all be leaving the mansion.
That makes sense.
- Oh, no, I'll be staying
right here on the premises,
so I won't be able
to accompany you.
- Wait a minute!
You're not gonna go with us?
Then how exactly are we
supposed to get there?
- [laughs]
- Huh?
- Guess you're pretty slow
on the uptake, aren't you?
- Uh...
Oh! I get it now!
So Otto's gonna get us
to the Sanctuary!
Because he thinks
that cooperating with Emilia
in any way possible
will give Roswaal,
- her backer, an overall...
- Hey, hold on a second!
- better impression of him.
- That's--
- Wait. Otto, is that right?
- Ugh! The purity
in Miss Emilia's innocent eyes
is killing me! Yes! I'm sorry!
That's exactly right!
- The way you wear
your ulterior motives
on your sleeve makes you
all the more likeable.
- Yeah, that's not
really comforting,
coming from somebody like you!
- I appreciate your help.
On that note, feel free
to tell the three of us
about the Sanctuary.
- Very well. As you wish.
What I'm about to tell you now
is the undisclosed location
of the Sanctuary of Clemaldy,
how to get to it,
and how to enter it.
Equally as important
is the name
of somebody you must not forget
as you travel there.
Beware of one
you will likely encounter
by the name of Garfiel.
Remember that name, while
at the Sanctuary
especially,
because he'll be the one
with whom you must exercise
the most care.
[birds chirping]
- Hey, Rem.
We're gonna be leaving now.
I told Frederica that she needs
to take extra special care
of you.
Wait right here for me, okay?
Hmm?
- You all set to go?
- Sure am, new recruit.
I see you're rockin'
that uniform already.
- You think so? [giggles]
What were you doing,
saying goodbye to Miss Rem?
- Yeah, something like that.
We're not planning on
stayin' out there very long,
but I wanted to see her
before I left.
Do me a huge favor,
and make sure that Rem
is well-taken care of
while I'm away, all right?
- Understood!
You can count on me!
- The ad about needing
a new maid
only went up two days ago,
and this is your first day
actually being in the mansion.
I'm pretty impressed you
found it without getting lost.
And I really admire
your decision
to leave your parents and home
at such a young age, too.
- I'm 12 years old!
I'm old enough
to be a working grown-up now!
Wait. I meant a working adult!
And I would appreciate it
if you'd treat me
more like an adult, too!
- Get better
at speaking politely,
and get Frederica
to fully initiate you,
and then I'll think about it.
- Hmm. I mean, yes, sir! I will!
- [chuckles]
- [gasps]
- Huh?
- I forgot
what a pain she can be
when she gets serious
about hiding.
- Is there really
a mysterious room in here?
- Yeah, it's Beatrice's.
I think you know her,
too, don't you?
So be sure to take care
of her also,
because you might randomly
bump into her
when you're opening a door
somewhere inside the mansion.
- Now hold on, Mr. Subaru.
Aren't you asking
a bit much of me?
- Yeah, you're right. I'm sorry.
But you're the only one
I can ask.
I hope you forgive me
for this.
- [giggling]
Oh, all right. If you insist.
I'll just have to find the time
to help you out, then.
- Thanks.
You're a big help, Petra.
EMILIA: Look after
the mansion for us.
Rem, Petra, and Beatrice,
too, all right?
- Yes, you can rely on me.
Please take care,
and be safe during your travels,
Miss Emilia.
And bring this with you.
It'll allow you to get past
the magical barrier
in the forest
and enter the Sanctuary.
From that point,
the ground dragons should be
able to take you
directly
to the location I
described.
- So the requirement
to get through the barrier
is that stone?
- [gasps]
- You have the location
and the capability,
so now you only need
the resolve and will.
- Frederica.
- Do take good care
of the Sanctuary,
and please don't forget the one
that I mentioned earlier.
- [grunts] We'll be watching out
for Garfiel. I promise you.
- Um, excuse me. Mr. Subaru?
- Hmm?
- I hope that you'll
accept this from me.
- I, uh...
- Lending a white handkerchief
to a traveler,
who later returns it
stained
and worn from his
journey
is an old custom.
It's thought to be
a sort of prayer
for safe travels
while he's away.
- Oh, it's one
of those things, huh?
Sure, I'd be happy to.
Thanks a lot, Petra.
- [squeals]
- I promise I'll return it.
- Uh...
- [whimpers]
- Hey, wait. Now what
randomly brought that on?
This sudden rebellious phase
is kinda making me sad.
- [giggles] Well, you should
hurry up and get going,
'cause the Lost Forest
of Clemaldy grows more dangerous
as the sun goes down
and nighttime approaches.
Safe travels,
and best of luck to you.
- [laughs] Goodbye, Subaru!
You'd better protect that lady!
You hear me?!
- Master, I did it exactly
as you instructed me to.
So now everything depends
on Miss Emilia
and how she handles
the Sanctuary.
There's nothing we can do,
but pray.
SUBARU: For real?
Puck isn't showing up?
- It feels so odd.
I've called out to him
several times,
and I can feel the link
from our contract, but...
- Has anything like this
ever happened before?
- Yes, but not very often.
There have been
a couple of times in the past
when he didn't show up
for a few days.
- [grunts]
- Take care of Lia for me.
I'm really counting
on you, okay?
- Couldn't have been...
- [gasps] Don't worry!
I have contracts
with lesser spirits, too,
and I can also fight with them
if the need arises,
so no matter what happens,
I can protect you!
- You're my knight
in shining armor!
- Hey!
- [laughs]
Frederica did warn us.
You remember?
She told us that something
might happen.
- Yes, to beware
of Garfiel, right?
- Uh-huh. And Roswaal
mentioned a few times
that he was gonna see him,
which seems kind of weird to me.
- [door slides]
- Excuse me!
We just made it to the forest!
[Frederica]
The Lost Woods of Clemaldy.
A special barrier there
protects the Sanctuary
from outsiders.
It makes them lose their way
to prevent them
from getting too close.
That's the reason it's come
to be known as the Lost
Woods.
- So the Sanctuary's
just up ahead of us.
[gasps]
- Hey, what's up, Mili?
Don't tell me you're
actually feeling nervous?
- Huh? How were you
able to tell that?
- [dramatic] Because I
know everything about you!
[normal] At least,
that's what I'd like to say,
but I'm pretty sure
anybody could tell.
[grunts]
- Uh...
[sighs]
Oh, you're right.
I'm sorry for worrying you.
It's just that we're
about to arrive
at a village
where only demihumans live.
- Oh, I understand.
Really sorry I wasn't
thinking that far ahead.
I suppose, in a place like that,
there might be more half-elves
exactly like you there, huh?
- To be honest with you,
I've never even seen
another half-elf before.
But, yes, maybe
in the Sanctuary, there'll be...
- Hey, don't worry.
Cause I'll--
[gasps]
What's going on here?!
- Uh, is this...
- Oh, crap. This can't be good.
I'm borrowing this!
- [Emilia thumps]
- [gasps]
Emilia!
[gasping]
What the hell? Where am I?
- [brush rustles]
- Huh?
[wind blowing]
Hey, who are you?
[gasps] Look at those ears.
Are you an elf?
No, hold on! Wait a minute!
[panting]
Hey! Is anybody there?!
If this is the Sanctuary,
someone answer me!
Look at this place.
[gasps]
[wind blowing]
[grunts]
[footsteps echoing]
[panting]
- [woman] I see.
- [gasps]
- So that's the root
of your desire?
How very interesting.
- [gasps]
[overlapping voices whispering]
- My apologies.
Did I startle you?
- [gasps]
[women vocalizing]
- It's been quite a long time
since I spoke with anyone,
so perhaps I was
a bit too eager.
My name is Echidna,
but that isn't my title.
Perhaps you would know me a bit
better as the Witch of Greed.
["Realize" playing]
[singing in Japanese]
♪ Realize ♪