My name is Echidna,
but that's not my title,
so perhaps you'd know me better
as the Witch of Greed.
- [gasps]
- It hurts to see you
look so alarmed by me.
Despite who I am,
I'm still a tender young maiden,
you know.
- Sorry, but...
there's no way
I'm not gonna be alarmed
when you tell me
that you're the Witch of Greed
the first moment
we meet each other.
- Ah, I see.
Well, that is a fair point.
[Echidna giggles]
- What is this place?
I was in some dark ruins
just a minute ago.
When did you move me?!
- I'm sorry, but unfortunately
you're quite mistaken.
You weren't physically moved
anywhere at all.
You were merely invited
to my tea party.
- Your tea party?
- Indeed.
It's a witch's tea party.
So are you just going
to stand there forever?
Why don't you at least
come over and sit down
before the tea gets cold?
- [gasps]
Ah, damn it! All right!
Yeah, fine! Whatever!
- Well, you're quite
the brave one, aren't you?
Downing tea served by a witch
in a single gulp.
- [scoffs] If you
really intended to kill me,
then I'd already be
a little pile of ash right now.
What kinda tea is this,
anyway?
'Cause it's a little bland.
- It's actually
something that's produced here.
To put it bluntly,
it's a body fluid of mine.
- What the hell did you
just let me drink?!
- [laughs] You're truly
a fascinating individual,
now, aren't you?
Standing there in front of me
like it's
a totally normal thing to do.
- Hah! You think
you're so pretty,
your beauty would make
a normal person's eyes fall out?
Yeah, right!
I'll have you know that my eyes
are blessed all day
long
by the prettiest girl
alive!
So give it up, all right?
No matter how many times
I look at you,
I'm not exactly gonna think
you're beautiful.
- No, most normal people tend to
vomit when they stand before me.
Pretty funny, isn't it?
- Yeah,
that's freakin' hilarious!
- [laughing]
- Now what is it
you want with me, anyway?
- Oh, nothing, really.
You've come here
completely of your own accord.
If you want to go back,
I can send you there,
but are you sure
that's what you want?
- Huh?
- This is an opportunity
to talk to the Witch of Greed.
It's not something
that just anyone,
other than you,
can earn quite so easily.
The only real requirement
to have a dialogue
is for both of us to exist,
so let's remove
the unnecessary things.
All we need are our words.
Let me affirm the desires,
the curiosities,
and the greed that you seek
to satisfy with answers.
- [woman vocalizing]
- [overlapping whispers]
Now, then, what is it
you'd like to ask me?
- [gasps]
- Do you want to know
about Daphne,
the Witch of Gluttony,
who created beasts
that defied the will of God
to save the world
from starvation?
Maybe you want to hear about
Carmilla, the Witch of Lust,
who granted emotions
to nonhumans
in an attempt
to fill the world with love.
Or about Minerva,
the Witch of Wrath,
who struck people to heal them
as she lamented the state
of her war-torn world.
Perhaps you're more curious
about Sekhmet,
the Witch of Sloth,
who drove a dragon
past the great waterfall
just for a chance to rest.
Or Typhon, the Witch of Pride,
who, out of innocence
and cruelty,
judged criminals
one after another.
Or Echidna, the Witch of Greed,
whose thirst for knowledge
led her to do things
she regrets, even in death.
But of course the price
of knowing everything
knows no bounds.
- [gasps]
Or there's the Witch of Envy,
who killed all the other witches
and used them as sustenance
while making the whole world
her enemy.
She is the most detestable
of them all.
[whispering stops]
Oh, what a shame.
It looks like
I've frightened you too much.
It's in a witch's nature.
Bothersome, isn't it?
- [gagging]
- Oh! That took less time
than I thought it would.
People who are compatible
really do adapt quickly.
- What are you talking about?
- The tea
that you drank earlier,
I used
the Envy Witch Factor on it
as a means to strengthen
your resistance a little bit.
Now you and I can talk
freely and leisurely.
So, then, what would you
like to ask me?
- That's enough!
You're not gonna
get away with this!
What did you do to my body?
- Please don't get
the wrong idea.
I didn't make you drink that tea
with the intention
of doing anything bad.
In fact, I find your existence
a rather desirable thing.
I'm a bit embarrassed, really.
- Huh?
- Sometime over these
past few days, you killed
the one who possessed the Sloth
Witch Factor, didn't you?
At the moment of his death,
the Witch Factor chose you
as its new dwelling.
That's also why you entered
this burial ground unharmed.
- This what? I'm in a cemetery?
- Mm-hmm. Where you're standing
is the Witch's Graveyard,
where my soul
is being held prisoner,
the Sanctuary.
- You're saying you know
where the Sanctuary is?!
- [gasps] I don't have
enough experience
to get a read on you yet.
Either you're somebody
who's incredibly brave
- or just very bold.
- Figure it out later!
Now what you're saying is
the forest
where those old ruins are,
where I was before you
zapped me here,
that is the Sanctuary?
- You're so mean.
But actually
you happen to be correct.
The Sanctuary
is just outside of the ruins.
So what other questions
would you like for me--
- And if I ask you to,
you'll let me back out, right?
- Y-Yes, absolutely.
I can guarantee that.
But isn't there anything else
you want to ask me?
'Cause now's your chance.
- Sorry, but I'd rather
meet up with Emilia outside
than spend another second here
talking to you.
- Huh? [gasps]
Wait! Y-You're kidding,
right?!
But I'm the Witch of Greed!
People from around the world
have come to me
in search of my knowledge,
very powerful people!
So relax, okay? We can just
sit down and talk for a while.
I have knowledge about the truth
of this world that no one-
- Not interested.
- [wails]
- I'll make it a point
to chat over tea with you
some other time
in the future, okay?
- [groans] You'd ask
a dead woman, a witch at that,
to agree
to delay our discussion
as if it were the simplest thing
in the world?
- [energy whooshes]
- [Subaru gasps]
ECHIDNA: I've never had
a tea party like this.
If you're really going back,
I'll just take
my compensation first.
- [gasps] Just so you know,
these days, I'm what
you'd call completely broke.
- Compensation for a witch
doesn't mean money.
What I desire from you
is to make a promise to me.
You'll tell no one of what
transpired at this tea party.
That is my condition.
And since
you insist on leaving,
I'll send you away
with a souvenir.
I've decided
to grant you the right
to face the Trial
of the Sanctuary.
- What are you talking about?
- You may not understand now,
but once you learn where it is,
you'll realize its true worth.
I wonder, what feelings
will you have towards me
when that happens?
The mere thought of it gives
me
such beautiful expectations.
[slurping]
[sighs]
- Well, that was freaky.
You really are a witch, huh?
- Without a doubt.
and I just so happen to be
a very, very evil magic user.
- [gasping]
[yelps]
[wind blowing]
[groans]
[gasps] All right,
I need to get out of here
and back to Mili and Otto.
I feel like someone
said something to me.
[gasps]
- [groans]
- [gasps] Otto?!
- Look at you, just waltzi''
out of there like that!
You've got some nerve, outsider!
Is this like a magmarin laughi''
when it's full of holes?!
- [yells]
- [grunts]
- [chuckles]
- [groans] Ow.
Damn it. What the hell? [gasps]
[gasps]
[sighs]
[man scoffs]
What a tantalizing choice!
Hey, that's
a nice ground dragon.
[Patrasche growls]
[snarls]
- Whoa! Easy!
- [both gasp]
- [snarls]
- Well, you're
a real good-lookin' girl now,
- ain't you, precious?
- [gasps]
- Come on.
I'm not gonna hurt you!
Just take a little nap!
You'd better thank her
for fightin' so hard for you!
- W-Wait. Wait!
- I'm gonna thrash you guys
and then throw you out
of this forest half-dead,
just alive enough to swear
you won't tell a soul
about this place!
- Hold on! You don't happen
to know Frederica, do you?!
- Why the hell did I
just hear that name
come out of your filthy mouth?
- Why the hell do you think?
Just stop this
for a minute, and--
Thought about it
and still don't know.
I guess I'll need
to bash your skull in first!
- Quit jumping to conclusions,
and listen to me!
It's because
we all know her, too, okay?!
- Huh?
- [gasps]
- The name's Garfiel,
and the pleasure's all yours.
Now, if you guys know her
like you say you do,
then you must've heard
that name before, right?
- Y-You mean you're--
- How in the hell do you know
that I have anything to do
with Frederica?!
- Uh, you're not
actually serious, right?
- I just got beat up
for nothing.
What am I supposed to do
with all
this pent-up anger inside?
GARFIEL: You ever shut up?
I apologized, didn't I?
OTTO: You call... [imitating]
"Hey, sorry, about that,
dummy.
Looks like I kinda
jumped the gun," an apology?!
GARFIEL: Eh, if you'd shown me
that thing sooner,
that woulda done it.
You gotta act on a ganglion
without thinkin'.
- A gangli--What was that?
- Judgin' by that hair,
I'm guessin'
that's the famous Emilia,
the silver-haired half-devil
that Roswaal's been helpin'
out.
- She's a half-elf, got it?!
So don't you ever call her
something like that again!
- Hah! Well, look at that!
I guess you can put some energy
into your voice after all.
Wanna know how it feels
to be a bazomazo
being flung back and forth?
- I gotta ask you something.
Is there
some sort of translation glitch
going on between you and me?
- Huh?
- [moans]
[sighs]
- Emilia, you're awake!
Oh, man. I'm glad you're okay!
- Subaru, where--
[gasps] Who are you?!
Just so you know,
I'm not going to let you
lay a single finger on him!
- Hang on, Mili!
I appreciate it,
but as a guy, I have
mixed feelings about this!
- I'm not gonna do anything,
'cause I don't want Ram
givin' me hell later on.
- What?
- Yeah, so, this guy's Garfiel.
- Hold on a minute.
You mean the same one that
Frederica was telling us about?
- Yep, that's right,
and he's showing us
the way to the Sanctuary.
We're headed out there now.
Uh, and that's where
the villagers
from Arlam and Ram are.
Isn't that what you told me?
- You don't wanna believe me,
that's your call,
but either way, there ain't
no turnin' back now, guys.
We've already made it
past the barrier.
- [gasps]
- Huh?
Then we're in the Sanctuary
right now?
- Come on. Gimme a break.
You of all people should know.
Weren't you asleep 'cause you
got too close to the barrier?
- What do you mean by--
Wait. When the stone glowed...
- That's exactly
when it happened.
So this pendant was reacting
to the barrier. Is that it?
Okay, but why did
only Emilia pass out?
I mean,
I got transported somewhere,
but Otto was here.
Why didn't the same th--
- [ Garfiel scoffs]
- [both gasp]
- Don't play dumb.
You know damn well
why the barrier reacted that way
to her and not both of you.
And it isn't only half-elves
that thing reacts to, either.
It works on me
and a lot of others, too.
Figure it out yet?
Is it because
you have mixed blood like I do?
- [chuckles]
- Let me make sure
I've got this.
So the Sanctuary is a place
where demihumans
with mixed blood live?
- That's right! Nice guess!
We welcome you here,
Miss Emilia,
and your escorts, too!
[Otto gasps]
GARFIEL:
Roswaal likes to go around
callin' this area the Sanctuary,
but it ain't really
the kinda place
that deserves
such a fancy title.
Nothin' there
but a ragbag of halfwits.
It's just
a dead-end testing ground.
- Um, where should we--[gasps]
- So you're finally back?
It took you long enough.
SUBARU: Ram!
- I've no clue
which Barusu you are,
but I'm disappointed by how long
it took you to get here.
Although I suppose I was a fool
to expect more of you.
- If your story is gonna be
you have no clue who I am,
then at least stick to it!
- Whatever.
- [growls]
- I would like to welcome you
to the Sanctuary, Miss Emilia.
Master Roswaal
is waiting inside.
Allow me to show you the way.
Garf, I want you to take
the ground dragon and carriage
somewhere suitable, all right?
- Now, is that
any way to treat me?
That's just
how I like it, though.
Okay, cabbie, follow me.
Are you referring to me?!
That's the worst name
you've called me yet!
And why do I have to be
alone with you?!
- I'll grab what's left of you.
OTTO: Why is everyone
so mean to me?
- Hey, what are
you talkin' about?
I'm not being mean.
When I was unconscious,
Emilia only stayed safe
because of you.
I'm grateful.
- Oh? Is that really true,
Mr. Natsuki?
Well, all right, then.
As long as you're appreciative.
See you soon!
- Too easy.
- [gasps]
- What's the matter?
- [gasps] Oh.
Uh, just wondering how you
were doing, that's all.
Remember what was going on
the last time I saw you?
I couldn't get in touch
with you after that,
and to be honest,
I was really worried.
- Well, as you can see, I'm
just
as lovely and healthy as ever.
And the villagers of Arlam
are all safe as well,
so don't worry.
- [sighs] That's good to hear.
But more than that,
it's a huge relief to me...
really.
Uh...
so listen. I, uh...
[sighs]
- Hey, Ram...
this isn't much of a place
to stand around and talk.
Would you mind
showing us inside?
- Oh, no. Not at all.
- Subaru, are you all right?
- Yeah.
- I'm sorry for interrupting,
but you just seemed to--
- No, it's okay. I get it.
I freaked out a little.
With all that's going on,
for her
to not even ask about Rem...
I'm pretty pathetic, huh?
- Hmm?
It's only natural
for you to feel frightened.
I'll never think
your having emotions
- is the least bit pathetic.
- [sighs]
- Come on. We've come this far,
so let's fix
what happened to Rem
and everything else, too.
Sounds good.
And no matter what happens,
you can count on me
to be your human shield
and keep you safe.
ROSWAAL: Ah, Miss Emilia
and dear Subaru.
Feels like it's been so very
long since I last saw you
both.
SUBARU: I was gonna slug you
when I saw you again, but
now...
What the hell happened?
EMILIA: What could have
hurt you like this?
- Well,
It's a rather long story.
Where shall I begin?
SUBARU: Hey, before that,
just one thing.
The alliance with Miss Crusch
is on now.
Are you satisfied
with the results you got
from ditching me?
- Oh, yes.
I feel most satisfied, indeed.
Truly, you were
the once-in-a-lifetime windfall
I had long waited for.
- Oh, really?
- Roswaal,
what exactly is this place?
- Since we got here--
No, since we made contact
with the barrier,
I've had this anxious feeling
in my chest. I can't relax.
Even though I've heard it
called the Sanctuary,
it really doesn't seem
like one to me at all.
In fact, it feels more like--
- More like a Witch's Graveyard?
Does it seem to make far more
sense for you to call it that?
- [gasps] Wh-What do you mean?
Exactly what I said,
nothing more, nothing less.
These are the very grounds
where the Witch of Greed Echidna
met her end
a long, long time ago,
and in my mind,
it's worth calling a Sanctuary.
- Echidna, huh?
- EMILIA: Subaru?
- [gasps]
- Are you all right?
- Uh, y-yeah, I'm fine.
And why are you
overseeing a place
that has
such a seedy back story, anyway?
- It's quite simple, really.
This land has been overseen
by the heads of the Mathers
family for generations now.
- So then the Mathers family
and the Witch of Greed have--
- It's Echidna.
- Huh?
- Please, when you speak of
her,
I do prefer you use her name.
"The Witch of Greed"
is rather unbecoming.
It makes her sound so sinister.
Not very nice, is it?
- Um, then the Mathers family
and Echidna
have been acquainted
for a long time,
and that's why they've
always overseen this place?
- Indeed,
although saying, "oversee,"
is a bit of an exaggeration.
The barrier here
does most of the work,
thwarting entry from outsiders
who don't follow procedure.
In addition to that, the barrier
triggers certain effects
on those whose blood
meets specific conditions.
I believe you experienced this
yourself, Miss Emilia.
- [gasps]
- That doesn't explain
how you got so jacked up.
You're bandaged in a bed,
recuperating.
- [sighs]
- Did you not find it the least
bit strange, Miss Emilia?
- Huh?
- That all the people
who fled to the Sanctuary
along with Master Roswaal
and myself
ended up remaining here instead
of returning to the mansion?
- Uh, oh, well, I...
You stayed around 'cause
you're hurt, didn't you?
- It's because
none of us can leave.
We're all being held
under house arrest
here in the Sanctuary.
- BOTH: Huh?!
- Myself, Ram,
the people of Arlam, everyone.
And I'm sure that goes
for the two of you as well,
trapped from the moment
you arrived.
- What the hell?
You guys are still
flappin' your gums in here?
- House arrest?
- So Roswaal's injuries are--
- Nope, not at all.
Roswaal here got hurt 'cause he
was rejected by the Trial.
- Wait. What?
- I don't understand.
- You've seen what happens when
you enter this place, right,
when you make contact
with the barrier?
Mixed-bloods who go through that
and still come inside,
you're stuck here forever
like the rest of us.
- [gasps]
Does that mean Emilia, too?
[Emilia gasps]
- The barrier doesn't mean
jack squat to most people,
which seems a little unfair
if you ask me.
Don't you think, Miss Emilia?
The only way to break it
is to go through
the Graveyard's trial.
But if anybody
who isn't a mixed-blood
tries to take it on...
All of the villagers
have been rounded up
in one place here.
Long as they don't act up,
we won't hurt 'em.
Even get food
and a place to sleep.
And that brings me
to our single demand.
Break the barrier.
The only one allowed
to go through the Trial
and make that happen is you.
If you can't,
we won't let any of
the villagers leave this place,
and you aren't gonna be able
to leave here, either!
Do you understand?
- [gasps]
- [villagers gasping]
- Subaru!
- Oh, thank goodness
you're safe!
- I'm glad you're all okay.
- What about the others?
Are they all right?
- Is the lord recovering
from his injuries?
We heard he got hurt
trying to help us.
- We're so relieved!
- Hey! Everyone, listen up!
In case you didn't know,
we got rid of the bad guy
who attacked the village.
[villagers murmuring]
The other group that evacuated
is back there now
waiting for all of you
to come home to them.
[villagers sighing]
- Guess every one of you
has already been told
that this isn't
the easiest place to get out of.
But don't you worry!
'Cause we've got somebody
who's getting ready
to face the trial head-on
and set you free!
- Wait. You mean...
- Are you gonna do it?
- No. If I could do it,
I'd be more
than happy to, but...
[villagers murmuring]
- You all know who this is,
Emilia, the royal
selection candidate.
She'll be undergoing the trial.
[villagers murmuring]
WOMAN: I don't know.
EMILIA: I'm sorry
you had to wait so long.
In the place of your
domain lord, Roswaal L. Mathers,
I will take on this challenge,
and I'd like your support!
[villagers murmuring]
ELDER: Let me ask you one thing.
- Chief.
- [murmuring]
- Why do this?
If I remember correctly,
you bowed your head to us
the last time you saw us, too,
but in that instance, we were
the ones who turned you away.
- [gasps]
- If you want to help us
so we'll all back you
in the royal selection,
we understand, and everybody
here thinks that's just fine,
so long as you say so.
But if you have some
other
reason for taking this
risk,
then we have a right to know.
We need to put our concerns
at ease and be assured
that you're not a witch
who's beyond our comprehension.
- [gasps]
- [grunts]
I understand that.
Right now, I'm not sure if I
can
give you a respectable answer.
I don't have
any convincing things to say,
nothing that's strong enough to
satisfy you with any confidence,
but although
it wasn't for very long,
I spent a few days
with your loved ones,
those who aren't here now.
Doing so made me realize that...
families should
always be together.
[crystal clinks]
And I want to do
everything I can
to make sure
you all return to yours.
I didn't promise any of them
that I'd do so,
but I did promise myself.
So that's why.
That's my reason.
I wasn't really thinking
about earning your support
or anything,
but if it's possible, I'd--
Well, I'd like...
to become your friend,
if that's okay.
- Miss Emilia.
- Uh, yes?
- I realize this may sound
like we only care
about what benefits us, but...
I pray you'll be our friend.
- [gasps]
W-Wait. I was--
I know that I'm not worthy,
but I humbly accept!
- "I'm not worthy," huh?
Who says that
in this day and age?
Ram: Interesting.
Miss Emilia seems
to have changed a bit.
Is it because of something
you said to her?
SUBARU: It's from her thinking
things through on her own.
It's not fair to her
to assume all her decisions
come from someone else.
- You're right.
Guess I was in the wrong
this time.
[wind blowing]
[singing in Japanese]
- How'd it go?
Were you able to get
enough support
from the lesser spirits?
- Uh-huh. Everything's fine.
Still, I think
I'd like one last cheer.
SUBARU: You really mean it?
- Yes, of course I do,
if you don't mind.
- You can do it!
Don't give up! E.M.C.!
Go, Emilia!
The major challenger!
- [giggles]
Thanks for that.
- [gasps]
- That light show
means she's been approved
as a qualified challenger
in the trial.
- This is it.
SUBARU: I get that it sucks
being trapped here,
but why didn't you
do this trial yourself?
- [scoffs]
If I could, I would, damn it.
- [gasps]
- H-Hey, is she gonna be okay?
- The lights
aren't supposed to go out
as long as the trial's going on.
- GARFIEL: What is this?
- Emilia, wait!
- Barusu!
- [panting]
- What the...
- I don't understand,
but if I can get inside,
that's good enough for me!
Just stay there!
I'll yell if I need you, okay?!
[gasps] Emilia!
SUBARU: First, you need
to face your own past.
[thump]
- Good morning, son!
- [groans]
- Hey, come on!
What's that all about?
What's wrong?
You look like you've
just seen your own dad
half-naked
first thing in the morning!