RAM: I was starting to wonder
if
you'd arrive before I got old.
SUBARU: Hold on a minute.
You're Otto's helper?
- It sounds like we're equals
if you call me that.
Try "attendant."
- Now you're talking
like
you're his witch's
familiar.
- [sighs]
- I received orders
from Master Roswaal
to help you,
but seeking out
the assistance of Otto
to try and meet that end
was my own decision.
- So he measured up
to your standards?
RAM: I knew I needed
to find someone, anyone, fast,
or you would die in vain.
- Hate to admit it,
but you're right.
- Don't talk like that!
- For a person
who's been confined,
you seem awfully composed.
- Huh?
- [both sigh]
- I did just have
a good laugh, right, Otto?
- [laughs]
- We're leaving here.
As long as Miss Emilia
is attempting the trial,
Garfiel will remain
in the graveyard,
and while he's distracted,
we'll escape.
- SUBARU: No.
- [gasps]
- That'll have to wait
'til later.
- Seriously?
- I'm not sayin' we won't go,
but I've got
a golden opportunity right now.
- What is it
you're planning to do?
- The same thing I was
trying to do three days ago
before I was interrupted.
["Realize" playing]
[singing in Japanese]
♪ Realize ♪
- Look, Roswaal,
I won't let you hide anything
from me this time.
- Reunited after
just three days.
It doesn't exactly feel like
a miraculous return, does it?
- No more jokes.
The last thing I wanna do now
is stand here and play these
annoying little games with
you.
- So Ram let you in, yes?
Well, after ordering her
to help you,
I suppose that would make sense.
- Yeah, which is why
she did it so easily this time.
I've put the idea of running
away on hold for the moment.
- Oh?
- I wanna ask you something,
assuming that my leaving
the Sanctuary is a given.
- By all means.
If I have the answer,
I won't even hesitate.
- As far as I know,
this is something only you
would be able to tell me.
So my question is,
is Beatrice...
a member of the Witch's Cult?
- Now, now.
What makes you suspect
she would be involved
in such a thing?
- I saw her in the library,
and she was holding a Gospel.
If I'm right about this
and she is a witch cultist...
then that would make her
an enemy to us all.
Or at least to me.
- Those are strong words,
words that took
true resolve to say.
However...
even if you speak them
with that pained expression,
they're not very convincing.
- [shudders]
- The idea that the two of you
would ever become enemies
is a truly awful one.
Thus, I feel I should
offer you a helping hand.
- You wanna help me?
That sounds like
one of the shadiest things
I've ever heard.
- Something that resembles
a Gospel rather closely
is indeed in her possession,
so I can see how you thought
it might be one.
But you have my word
that she is not a witch cultist.
- [gasps] Are you sure?
- While her book isn't a Gospel,
it is somewhat unique.
That magical text
tells the true future,
and only two copies exist
in the whole world.
In fact, it's the closest thing
there is to the Tome of Wisdom.
- So what you're
saying is that--
Now hold on a second!
She definitely told me
that book was a Gospel!
- Everything I do
is in accordance
with the Gospel's guidance,
I suppose.
- That's because
it lacks an official name,
hence it shares the same
one
as the defective versions.
- Defective? [grumbles]
Well, just as long as she's
not really a witch cultist,
then it's all right.
But now what I want to know
is how am I ever gonna
convince her to help me.
Tell her, "Roswaal said
to ask the question."
- Huh?
- If you relay that exact
instruction to Beatrice,
she should respond.
- That sounds just like...
- Look her in the eye and say,
"Roswaal said
to ask the question."
- [gasps]
- Ah, I see.
It appears that these words
are insufficient for you,
aren't they?
- Uh, hang on. I don't know
what you're talking about.
- Well, in that case,
tell her this,
"I am that person,"
and that should do the trick.
- What's that supposed to mean?
Get Beatrice
to ask the question.
Then answer it affirmatively.
If you do that, she will,
without a doubt,
stand by your side as an ally.
But how can you be so sure
that'll actually work?
- Because it's there
in the contract
that she holds so dearly
and is powerless to override.
- And you're certain about this?
All right,
but if this doesn't work,
you're getting
a punch in the face!
And that I can promise you.
Understand?
- [chuckles]
Oh, very well, then.
Do as you please.
Once you've joined forces
with Beatrice,
I can assure you
she'll be a great help
in solving all the problems
concerning the Sanctuary.
- Hey, Roswaal,
I've got one last question
for you.
- What would that be?
- Tell me the truth.
You're not actually
our enemy now, are you?
- No, of course not.
Rest assured.
I am an ally to you.
[door rattles]
OTTO: Did you get any answers?
- Quite a few.
I think all the pieces
fit together now.
What's the plan?
- A carriage
might draw attention,
so you and I will need
to ride out of here together.
Is that all right?
- Yeah. You'd be in danger
if you stayed around, too,
so that would--
Wait. Hang on a second!
Once we're out of the Sanctuary,
our first stop is the mansion,
and we can't
just leave Frederica there
to fend for herself,
but two of us
wouldn't be much help.
- In a fight, I'd have to agree.
Let me guess, then.
You're hoping
that I'll go with you, right?
- Well, it does seem
like the best way for us--
I mean, I'd feel a lot better.
- I suppose I must.
- [gasps]
Sure you don't mind?
Master Roswaal gave me
an order to assist you,
so this definitely
qualifies, but...
how will this work?
There's just one ground dragon
and three of us.
SUBARU: Uh...
- Even if the two of you
only amount to half a man,
you each take up
a whole man's space.
I don't think we'll all
fit on a single dragon.
OTTO: Was the "half a man"
comment necessary?!
GARFIEL: Havin' a cozy
little chat out in the woods?
Well, since I'm here,
why not let me in on the fun?
[Patrasche growls]
- [scoffs]
Like they always say,
"The brighter it shines,
the farther away
the magrizza goes," ya know?!
SUBARU: Don't you have
a trial to oversee right now?
Why are you wasting time,
hangin' around here?!
- You keep your mouth shut!
My job is to protect this place,
so if it's bein' threatened,
I got all the time in the
world.
As long as you're out here,
you'll never escape
the eyes of the Sanctuary!
- What are you talking about?
- Let's just say
your little plans were leaked.
So where do ya think
you're headin' off to?
Well, speak up!
[both gasp]
- We're taking Barusu
outside the Sanctuary.
He'll only cause you trouble
if he stays here,
so it's best for everyone.
It all works out perfectly.
- Think you know
what's goin' on in my head, huh?
Damn, ain't nothin' lovable
about you at all.
That is what I like
about you, though.
SUBARU: I-In that case,
is it safe to assume
you're gonna agree to let us go?
- Huh? Are you kiddin' me?!
Listen up, you blabbering idiot!
I know damn well it'd be a pain
in my ass to keep you out here!
Which means..
- Hoshin was Banan's sunset.
- [gasping]
- Seriously?
I don't understand those
expressions of yours at
all,
but just as long as--
Wh-What's up with you guys
all of a sudden?
- Given your lack of education,
it's no wonder
you didn't understand him.
- "Hoshin was Banan's sunset"
is a saying
based on the tale of how
the legendary trader, Hoshin,
brought the small nation
of Banan to ruin.
It gives your rival two options,
surrender or face
an all-out attack!
- Sounds like I was
better off not knowing that.
- Garf, are you so dumb
that you didn't
comprehend what I said?
- You may be hot, Ram,
but I am getting
pretty tired of your mouth.
Watch it.
[both gasp]
- Just 'cause
I'm crushin' on you,
don't mean I won't twist
your little arm off.
Now take him back
to where he was!
- You really don't want me
to leave, do you?
Like she said,
keepin' me around is bad news.
so if you can let me go without
any trouble, why wouldn't you?!
- I don't know
what the hell you are!
That means I can't
let you outside of this place,
and that's all there is to it!
- I hate to hear you say that,
as your decision may
greatly upset Master Roswaal.
Because to my dear master,
Barusu...
is simply a useless employee
and easily discarded.
- Gee, thanks a bunch!
I appreciate it!
- Why would it bother me
if Roswaal was upset?!
How much do you think
he cares about this place
or about the old hag
or anybody else, huh?!
He doesn't give a damn,
not even about you, Ram!
- Master Roswaal is--
- Shut up! Shut up! Shut up!
[creaking]
I don't give a shit
about that smug bastard.
I'm done arguing about this,
so hand him over now!
I'll tie him up and--
- Now, Ram?
- Go!
- [gasps]
- Damn you, small fry!
- [yells]
You can't afford to let
yourself get distracted, Garf.
- Just get the hell
out of my way, Ram!
- Hang on a minute, Otto!
What's happening?!
- You would have been
in big trouble
if we'd stayed there any longer!
Ram and I
made this decision together!
[whistles]
- Uh, hey,
what are you doing now?
- Something that I
was really hoping
I'd never have to resort to.
It would have been better
if this wasn't necessary!
- [gasps]
No, it can't be.
Are those the people of Arlam?
- What did I tell you?
I have
some very reliable helpers!
- I figured you only meant Ram.
- Be careful,
and stay safe, Subaru!
- Over this way!
The path is clear!
- Otto, take good care
of him for us!
- But why are they all
doing somethin' so crazy?
- You're the last person
who should be asking
a question like that!
- Just keep going straight,
and you'll find the barrier.
SUBARU: What about you guys?
- We'll hold 'em off.
- We can buy enough time
for you to escape, no problem!
- [roar]
[both gasp]
[all scream]
[rumbling]
- [gasping]
[footsteps booming]
[shudders]
- [growls]
[roaring]
- [gasps]
- [roaring]
- Please, Garfiel, no.
- [growling]
- Please...
don't hurt them.
I'll do as you say.
- [gasps]
SUBARU: So please...
don't harm anyone else.
[shuddering]
- [growling]
- You idiot! Get away from him!
- [roars]
- [gasps]
Garfiel!
- [roars]
- [screams]
[footsteps booming]
- If you know
what's good for you,
you'll stay away from Subaru,
you evil monster!
- Don't.
[Patrasche coos]
SUBARU: No! Stop killing them!
No one needs to die but me!
That's enough.
Leave me, Patrasche!
[gasps]
[yelps]
[stone clinks]
[energy whines]
[gasps]
[water dripping]
What the--Why am I here?
[gasps]
- [footsteps shuffling]
- It's morning.
Damn it.
How long have I been asleep?
[gasps]
Huh?
- [panting]
- [footsteps crunching]
What's going on?
[gasps]
[no audible dialogue]
No, I've gotta keep moving!
I have to get them back,
whatever it takes.
I don't get it.
Where is everybody?
[sighs]
[footsteps crunching]
Eh?
- [chitters]
- A rabbit?
How's this
the only living thing I've seen?
[gasps]
[gags]
[screams]
[chorus vocalizing]
[groaning]
[sobbing]
[gasping]
- [chittering]
- [screaming]
[silence]
- [chorus vocalizes]
- [gasps]
[gasps]
[shivers]
[groans]
- Why?
- [thumping]
[panting]
Why? Why?
Why? Why? Why? Why?
[wails] Why?!
ECHIDNA: You have earned
the qualification once again.
I invite you
to a witch's tea party.
It's quite rare for someone
to attend one of my tea parties
a second time.
You should be proud.
- [gasps]
I'm feeling so calm and relaxed.
This is creepy.
What is happening to me?
- It's due to the tea
you drank last time.
The contents therein
had a direct impact
on your Sloth Witch Factor,
encouraging stability.
If not for that,
your soul itself
would have crumbled to pieces.
Now I'm all ears and ready to
accept your words of
gratitude.
- Then can I assume
that this will keep on working,
even after I'm back outside?
- Well, we are talking
about your mental state, right?
As long as you remember
what happened here,
you should be absolutely fine.
Still waiting for a "thank you."
- Tell me...
is there any way that you know
of to try and overwrite the
vow?
- Hmm?
- You know, the one
that makes me
forget all about you
the minute I step outside.
Because as long as it stands,
my soul's still likely
to fall apart.
- I suppose that's true, but I--
- On top of that, my soul
isn't the only problem
here.
I still want to be able
to remember you, regardless.
- Huh?
- [slams table]
- And if that comes
at a price, fine.
I'll pay whatever you want.
- [gasps]
- In return,
I want assurance you won't
hide yourself in my memories.
- Uh, sure.
- Huh?
Really?! Thanks a lot!
And no changing your mind,
all right?!
- No, of course not. I wouldn't
ever do something so shameless,
though I will say
I think it's a bit unfair
to even presume that.
- [sighs]
Hmm.
- Gulping down
my body fluids again, are you?
[gags] I forgot!
- I'll ask you once more.
Where's the gratitude?
- [coughing]
- I'm waiting patiently,
but I don't think
I've heard it yet.
- Whatever! Thanks for making me
this nasty bodily-fluids tea,
you witch!
- I'm afraid that only wounded
my maidenly heart.
- [grumbles]
Uh...
[gasps]
- Anything else?
Something on your mind?
- Quit playin' around.
Exactly how much have you
found out about me, anyway?
- If that's your query,
I know only what I know.
If you're asking
what I want to know,
the answer is
everything in this world.
- There's no way
you aren't feeling strange
about all of this.
I have to assume, for you,
this is happening
right after your last tea party
with me, isn't it?
So if you don't think
this is strange, then...
that means...
- That means what?
- It means
you're not thrown by any this,
because you know
how it happened.
[gasps]
- Well, test me, then.
- [gasps]
[sighs] You might
not even have enough time
to regret saying those words.
- If that proves to be true,
can I expect you to break down
physically and emotionally
and cry over my corpse?
- [gasps]
Echidna...
I...
I've been Returning by Death!
Eh...
[gasps]
- You know...
it feels a bit embarrassing
to have you
staring at me like that.
Wh-When I--When I die,
I go back in time
and restart the world,
and it's happened a lot.
I call it "Return by Death."
- I heard you.
And before I heard you,
I saw you.
- I die, and I come back.
Return by Death.
- Return by Death!
- Hey! Take it easy!
Look, I understand how you feel,
but there's no need to--
- It's true!
I've been Returning by Death!
I've died and started again
over and over! Got it?!
- I Return by Death!
- I get it, I said!
- Just listen to me for a minu--
- I...
[crying]
Returned by Death...
starting again...
over and over.
[crying]
I...
All this time...
ever since I came
to this world...
I've never, ever been able
to say it to anyone.
Over and over...
all alone,
alone this whole time!
I--[sobbing]
- I know.
I know every single step
you've taken on your path here.
I was watching you.
But watching is all I was doing.
So if you don't mind,
I'd like you
to tell me yourself
what you've been thinking
and how you've felt,
the good and bad,
how much weight
you've carried, too.
I want to know everything.
That's what truly drives me.
Omniscience is
what I desire most.
After all...
I am the Witch of Greed,
Echidna.
[music playing]