- So you made it
past all those barriers
with the single goal of
entering the castle of dreams?
How very rude of you.
- [Subaru gasps]
[shadow warbling]
Seriously, what the hell
is your problem?
What is it you want
from me, anyway?
- For so long...
for so very long now...
I've been deeply
in love with you...
and nobody else.
- Don't say that.
- I love you.
You have to stop this.
- I have loved you, only you
for such a very,
very long time.
- No! I said stop, damn it!
[panting]
You and Echidna are insane!
I've had it!
I've had it with you both!
I won't let
anybody here help me!
I'll figure
everything out myself!
Now just leave me alone!
- So you're just gonna
keep on dying, starting over,
and making everyone cry?
That's your big plan, huh?
Must be pretty nice.
No matter how other people feel,
you can always make the excuse
that you're the one
who's suffering the most.
- Are you saying...
that I'm pretending to be
some kind of tragic hero?!
- That's not it.
I'm saying that deciding
you're the only one
who should be suffering
is cowardly.
That kind of twisted thinking
makes you a lot more despicable
than any witch.
- [gasps]
- And above all else...
it's incredibly
ungrateful to her.
SUBARU: Despicable?
Ungrateful?
You're kidding, aren't you?
Don't you get it?
You're the one who made me
like this in the first place!
All the pain,
all the torment, everything,
it only happens to me!
If I'd done nothing,
would things be different now?
Either way, I'm stuck
with a horrible future!
Who else but me would have
made these choices, huh?!
Who else would have done
the things that I've done?!
- You're hurt.
- [gasps]
- Please don't be hurt now,
and please don't suffer.
Please,
you mustn't look so sad.
- You have the nerve to say...
- Please don't hurt.
Just know love.
- That's what it comes down to?
Are you honestly that desperate
for me to love you?!
- Not at all.
You need to love
yourself more.
- Wh--
What the hell did you just say?
- Don't be hurt. Don't grieve.
Overcome those feelings,
and treasure yourself more.
- Are you serious?
You're the one
who gave me the ability
to Return by Death!
- I love you. That's why.
It's the very reason I want
you
to love and protect yourself.
- If I lost this power
out of love for myself,
I know for a fact
I wouldn't have
a thing left to offer anyone!
Other than my own life,
there's nothing I can use.
As long as I get hurt
more than others
and do whatever I can
to try and protect them,
I can be sure that nobody else
will ever have to suffer!
It's not like anyone cares
what happens
to a loser like me, right?!
No matter how badly
I get beaten up,
as long those around me
make it to the future
and we can start tomorrow
without losing others
in the process, then...
[crying]
Who am I kidding?
Rem's still gone.
If I'd just been stronger...
if I'd put myself
on the front lines
without worrying
about what might happen to me...
I could have prevented it.
I don't want...
to lose anyone else
the way I lost Rem!
[sobbing]
SEKHMET: And what is this
going to accomplish?
Look at you, crying, wailing,
trying to handle
everything on your own,
acting exactly like...
a helpless little child
who's feeling lonely.
- [crying]
- Baru...
why are you sobbing like that?
Seems like you're
really in pain.
You're hurting, you poor thing.
Who did this to you?
Who made you cry?
[shadow warbling]
I love you so much.
I hope you know that.
- Please, stop it.
- And the reason I love you
is because
you gave me everything.
Don't you see? That's why....
- Stop it!
- Huh?
Baru?
- [gags]
- I see.
Well, that's most certainly
one option, Subaru Natsuki.
- [gags]
MINERVA: His tongue.
You complete moron!
- [wails]
- [shatters]
- This'll be a piece of cake!
- [grunts]
- Out of the way, Typhon!
- Baru made
his own choice, okay?!
You stay out of the way, Nerva!
- I will not let
self-harm, suicide,
or murder happen in my presence!
[slams]
- [gasps] Sekhmet, why?
Emotionally,
something's compelling me
to take the boy's side also.
It's that simple.
And of course that would mean
I happen to be
on Typhon's side, too.
[sighs]
- [gasps]
[Satella gasps]
Why haven't you realized
that you should be included
among the ones you wish
so desperately to save?
It should be obvious.
[music playing]
[echoing] What could you
have possibly seen
in those two trials
that affected you this way?
KENICHI: And do
the best you can. Got it?
NAHOKO: Take care of yourself.
SUBARU: I...
JULIUS: I'd hoped...
the two of us
could have become friends.
WILHELM: Damn it.
Why did you die so easily?
Mr. Subaru, you are...
SUBARU: No matter
what I believe...
BEATRICE: I knew you couldn't
be "that person" for me.
SUBARU: no matter
what I wish for...
REM: Show me how awesome
you can be, Subaru.
Show them all.
[heart beating]
EMILIA: Thank you, Subaru.
Thank you for saving me.
SUBARU: I don't want to die.
MINERVA: See?!
That's how you truly feel!
[slam]
- [groans]
[coughing]
[panting]
[wind blowing]
[shudders]
Is there any--
any worth to my life at all?
What can I do now,
other than die and come back?
Can--Can I really believe...
that the people I care about...
also...
care for me?
SATELLA: I'll allow it.
- [gasps]
- You are the one
who rescued me,
so it would seem only fair
to grant you
the same opportunity.
I want you to know salvation.
Yes. That is my wish.
- [shudders]
[crying]
- Well, Minerva aside,
I have to admit I'm
actually a bit more surprised
by the way you two acted.
- [sighs] Just stay
out of this, Daph!
- [sighs]
- When I last spoke to him,
Subarun made
some pretty big boasts to me.
It might be selfish,
but I'd love to see him
at least try
to follow through on them.
- Quite an intriguing thought,
indeed.
And, Carmilla,
I'm fairly certain
that it was you
who called him back
from the brink of death itself,
now, wasn't it?
You even implemented
Faceless Bride
to ensure that,
but whatever for?
- No reason.
I just think that...
l-love is important.
Even if he doesn't
want to see it...
th-there is love there.
I know it.
And, uh, to me...
it shouldn't be taken
and not returned.
Sekhmet and Typhon
stepped forward
to make sure
his wishes were respected,
Minerva healed him,
Daphne prolonged his life,
and Carmilla used her Authority
to make him aware
of the love he couldn't see.
So while each of you may have
your own reasons for doing so,
it's quite clear that you all
wish to help Subaru Natsuki.
[laughs]
Absolutely fascinating.
Wouldn't you say?
SUBARU: Seriously...
what's the deal
with all of you?
'Cause I can't
understand or agree
with almost any
of your reasons for backing me.
It's no wonder
they call you witches.
- Since you've gone back
to vilifying us,
is it safe to assume
you've recovered your strength?
- I don't know
how to answer that now.
I'm at a loss.
- If that's truly the way
you're feeling at the moment,
then I'd like to inquire
about something.
If I were to lend you
my assistance,
you can be assured that
you'll arrive at a future
in which you save those
in need of being rescued.
And since you find yourself
not knowing what you should do,
then would you consider
extending your hand to me?
With everything in my power,
I'll take you
to the future you're
longing for without fail.
I give you my word.
Echidna...
to be perfectly honest,
I'm frightened of getting hurt.
I hate suffering, pain,
sadness, and being afraid.
I just don't want to feel
that kind of misery,
and I don't want anyone else
having to experience
those things, either.
I'm not ready to die.
Since sacrifice
is a prerequisite
to taking your hand,
that's something
I can no longer do.
If there's even a chance
I might have value to them
beyond my own death,
I'm gonna look for it,
no matter what.
If I can find it,
I have a feeling
I can repay them in some way
other than just dying.
- That path
is lined with thorns.
If you thought of your death
as a tool,
your heart would be all that's
necessary to offer as payment.
But trying to deny that
in an attempt to claim
not only your heart,
but the future
of other people as well,
would be exceedingly difficult
and, above all...
terribly greedy.
- I won't pretend
that you haven't saved me.
You've done it
time and time again.
Regardless
of what you had in mind
when you did it,
that part is undeniable.
- That poor Garfiel
is pitifully dimwitted,
and he's petrified
of the outside world.
You'll need to break that spell
if you ever hope to release him
from his circumstances.
- You're helping me?
- It's nothing.
I'm just being
a sore, meddling loser.
I wouldn't want you
getting the ridiculous notion
that all of the other witches
you've met
are actually good at heart
and that only
I was evil to the end.
Do keep in mind
that I am a girl,
one just so who happens to be
terribly fond of you.
- As far as I'm concerned,
every single one of you
is a monster
beyond comprehension.
I don't think we'll ever
understand each other,
and I doubt
I could ever like you, but...
thanks for being willing
to let me die.
- [sighs]
- [slurps]
- And for not letting me die.
- I appreciate it.
- Hmph!
- I'm grateful
you let me hear the voices
of those I needed
to hear the most.
For all you've done, thank you.
As I said, you're someone
I can't understand,
but it's a fact that I've been
saved by the power you gave me
more times
than I can even count.
Is Return by Death
still something
that's available to me?
If not relying on it too much
is what it takes to love
myself,
then I don't know.
That definitely
isn't gonna be easy.
But I will try to like myself
a little more now,
exactly the way you asked me to.
- Are you sure?
- Yeah.
I mean,
compared to dropping dead,
that's not such a tall order.
[creaking]
SATELLA: Listen.
Don't fret all alone.
Fight alongside
the ones who care about you.
Rely on each other.
Never forget
that it's those people
and others you've affected
who will grieve when you die.
- I'll remember.
There will be a day...
when I'll need you...
[echoing]
to come and take my life.
- [echoing] You have my word...
I'm going to save you.
[gasps]
[insects chirping]
Glad to see you, too.
[groans]
- Oh, you're awake.
- Eh?
Otto?
This is...
I'd normally be inside.
Did you carry me out?
- No, that was all Patrasche.
She started thrashing around,
and then the minute
that I released her
from the carriage...
- Wait.
You get rejected
from the graveyard
without being qualified.
Why would you try
a crazy thing like that?
I mean, I would
have come outside
just as soon as I woke up,
so why did you save me?
- [squeals]
- Oh, come on.
You really have no idea why?
- Huh?
- [purrs]
- [sighs]
- [grunting]
- Well, of course. Yeah.
I would never dream of it.
- Do you understand her?
What did Patrasche tell you?
She just said,
"Don't make me explain it,"
so I better not.
But I can't believe
you still need me to!
- Huh?
- [sighs]
Let me put it this way.
Leaping to save somebody
when you think
that they're in danger,
helping them out even if
it means risking your own life,
it's simple. To me,
the feelings behind them
are exactly the same,
which is something
that holds true
whether you're a human
or a ground dragon.
- Uh...
- Wow.
Pretty dense, aren't you?
Just forget about it.
[gasps] Wh-What's wrong?
- Why are you crying?
- Sorry!
It's not what you think.
[crying] It's just the timing.
I see, Patrasche.
You actually like me, huh?
I never thought you'd be
the first one
I learned that from.
Well, I like you, too.
Thank you.
- [squawks]
- Are you all right?
Wh-What happened in there?
- Were you worried?
Hey, hold on a second.
Does that mean
you like me, too?
- Okay, there's no need
for things to get awkward.
I'm only thinking
of what comes next!
- Yeah, I know.
We are friends, after all.
- [gasps]
[sighs]
- Mr. Natsuki?
- So does this mean
I managed to pass
the second trial somehow?
- [force hums]
- [groaning]
[gagging]
- What happened?
- Damn it. What was...
Wait. It rejected me?
Could I have lost
my qualification?
But why is that?
[no audible dialogue]
What a nasty little...
- I'm still so lost.
Is there anything I can--
- Listen, there's something
that I've gotta do.
Now I want you to take Patrasche
back down to the carriage.
- But--
- Please, Otto.
- [grunts]
[fire crackling]
- A way to leave the Sanctuary
without going
through the graveyard?
My, that's certainly
a brazen suggestion.
I believe we may have spoken
of this before, haven't we?
It's the first time
that we've discussed this.
We've interrogated
each other so often now,
it'd be pointless
to even try and count.
- Is that so?
It would appear you have
quite the history with me,
don't you?
- Well, yeah. I've also learned
about a lot of other stuff, too,
like the facility Ryuzu's in
or even the fact that
Garfiel's
actually an Apostle of Greed.
My goodness,
that is splendid indeed!
But foregoing the graveyard
seems awfully cowardly,
as far as I'm concerned.
Any particular reason
to be acting with such haste?
- No, of course there's not.
It's just...
I can't stand watching Emilia
getting hurt over and over.
- But that is precisely
what you're for.
- [winces]
- Surely you're
not trying to tell me
that it would pain you
to undergo it for her?
- What? That's--
- Not the case?
Are you so certain?
If you love Miss Emilia,
then it should be
a simple task for you.
What is best for her
should come first
and your needs after.
- Am I wrong?
- But, I...
- Never forget
that it's those people
and others you've affected
who will grieve when you die.
- [gasps]
- [sighs] Rather disappointing.
It would seem that you still
haven't the fortitude
necessary
for the task you've been given.
Only a sliver.
Yes, I had only
a tiny sliver of hope
that maybe, just maybe
I would finally be able
to see the future I desired.
But it's clear
that you've yet to even stand
at the starting line
of your resolve.
- [gasps] What is it
you're trying to say to me?
'Cause I have no idea
what you're talking about!
- What do you think I--
- I expect you to possess
the determination
to carry out your objective,
even if it means trampling
on Miss Emilia's will.
- [gasps]
- Understand?
In my estimation,
if you do it all for her sake,
it stands to reason
that sometimes
you must ignore
the things she wants.
A child dreaming
of childish things
is simply incapable
of the conviction needed
to walk through the hell
that you must choose.
- But that's totally backwards,
isn't it?!
If it's for Emilia, then--
- Listen. There is life.
- [gasps]
- So long as there is life,
there is a future.
So long as there is a future,
there is hope.
So long as there is hope,
there is great possibility.
And with possibility,
people can still be saved.
Am I wrong?
- [gasping]
- You have nothing to say
in response to this, I take it.
Unfortunate.
How many more times
must you disappoint me?
In any case, while you continue
to work on honing
your intention,
I'd like a moment to press you
on one more matter.
- Hmm?
I believe you've already faced
many of the problems that arise
within the grounds
of this Sanctuary.
Although there are some
that aren't limited
to the Sanctuary alone.
- Y-You mean the mansion, right?
Are you telling me
you know about what ha--
- Of course I do.
After all, the order given
for the assassins to attack...
that command was one
that I personally issued.
- [gasping]
Wait.
Just hang on a second.
It was you?
- I sent assassins
to the mansion
to help sharpen your resolve.
- You what?
- Even with
the Authority that you have
at your disposal,
it's infeasible to save both.
You must weigh the options
and decide
which is more important.
Once you make that choice,
you can never take it back.
Eventually,
you will be perfected
as a being who can only
rescue one and no others.
[no audible dialogue]
- Y-You're seriously insane.
- Yes, indeed.
And I've been that way
for quite some time now.
From the moment I was enchanted
by those eyes 400 years ago,
It's fair to say
that I've been rather unhinged.
- 400 years ago?
- Now I'm curious, Subaru.
After all that's
transpired,
why aren't you insane
yet?
To face seemingly
impossible circumstances,
to walk the path of solitude,
the human heart
is only an impediment.
So I've made the decision
to force it upon you.
What now, then?
What is it you hope to do?
- Please.
Please forgive me. I beg you.
It was--
It was all my fault, so--
- You must get off your knees
and raise your head, Subaru.
Nothing is your fault.
- This is--
- You're wrong!
I want to do what you said,
but I can't. I lost
my qualification for the trial.
- You what?
- Please.
Sending assassins to the mansion
won't do any good.
No matter who dies, it won't--
So please...
[creaking]
- I refuse.
- [gasps]
- I now see
an even greater need to do so.
Echidna will surely restore
your qualification.
If you earnestly wish to
receive it, then just ask her.
That's just the nature
of her avaricious personality.
You're still able to fix this.
You only need her assistance.
Therefore, my actions
will not change.
I will continue to corner you,
to strengthen your focus
until I deem you
as one who's perfected.
- [shuddering]
- Don't get conceited
about this.
You're not the only one
who understands
how Echidna's mind works.
- If--If you hate me,
punish me alone.
- You think
that's how I feel about you?
I could never hate you.
Of that, you can be certain.
You're my beacon of hope.
The only ones who allow me
to experience even a
flicker
of that sentiment at all
are you and Rem.
From the very bottom
of my heart,
I believe in you.
- I will...
I will never be like you.
I have my humanity.
Got that?
And I always will.
[wind blowing]
[running footsteps]
[panting]
Damn it! Damn it!
- [branch snaps]
- [yelps]
[groans]
So what do I do now?
What can I do?!
What do I do?
What do I do? What do I do?
What do I do?!
What do I do?! What do I do?!
OTTO: Hey!
Would you like me to tell you
- what you should do?
- [gasps]
["Memento" playing]
- Otto?
- That's me. Hello there,
and good morning to you.
Now, are you ready
to answer my question?
- Morning? Uh...
what are you doing here?
- Let's put that aside
for the moment.
I think we need
to talk about you first.
'Cause you were
muttering deliriously
and looking like
you were about to die.
- Are you serious?
- Yeah.
- I see.
Man, you always seem to find me
when I'm
in the freakiest states.
- Well, what can I say?
I am a trader, after all.
- Sorry, but I don't have time
right now to mess around.
Give me a second, okay?
I need to think.
You were feeling
hopeless, right?
And you wanted to know
what it is that you should do?
Just leave it to me.
- What do you mean?
Leave what to you?
- Listen, this is gonna take
a little preparation.
- Preparation?
Right. First off,
you're gonna need to take
a long, deep breath, okay?
- Huh?
- Quickly, now.
- [breathes deeply]
[inhales]
[grunts]
Huh?
- That's enough.
Stop putting on
a tough-guy front
around your friends,
Subaru Natsuki!
[wind blowing]