[mabeasts squeaking]
[metal clanking]
- Fantastic. Yes!
- [yells]
- Seems you've already...
- [winces]
[yells]
- [gasps]
That hurt.
This is pain,
and it makes me feel so alive.
- Damn it.
This shit ain't funny anymore.
The Boss did say this bitch
wouldn't lay down
and die easy, but still...
- Do you have disdain
for women who are like me?
All my wounds heal instantly,
meaning that I can
go on fighting forever.
It's quite pointless,
don't you think,
facing one
with such an ability?
- Don't be stupid!
I'll keep kickin' your ass
over and over,
no matter
how many times you heal.
- How wonderfully exquisite,
which is what makes it so sad.
- Huh?
- You sense the presence
of mabeasts, don't you?
And it seems someone else
is here besides your
sister.
Isn't your anxiety dulling
the force of your attacks?
[mabeasts squeaking]
Hah! Like hell, it is!
I'm not worried about Boss
or his buddy.
No matter how many mabeasts
go after him,
he's just gonna laugh
and send each and every one
of those bastards flyin'!
- Nope! Nope! Nope!
No way in hell!
[whimpers]
[mabeasts squeaking]
[all panting]
- Did letting Garfiel
work by himself backfire on us?
- Oh, come on! Try not to sound
so discouraged about everything!
I mean, you never know.
He might be out there right now,
screaming that we're
all just fine.
- Hey, you all right?
- Uh...
- [sighs]
[Subaru sighs]
I guess it's time to make use
of my unparalleled knowledge
of the modern world.
[mabeasts squeaking]
[guiltylowe growling]
[dramatic music playing]
[roaring]
- Bring it on,
you oversized mutt!
- [roars]
- [grunts]
[chorus vocalizing]
- [growls]
- Ready for a little science?!
Dust explosion!
[winces]
- [growls]
- Oh, crap!
OTTO: What did I tell you?!
Instead of doing weird
stuff
like whatever that was...
PETRA: It's faster to do this!
- I spent all the money I had
on this top-quality oil,
so you better appreciate it!
- [roaring]
- [gasps]
[yelps] You gotta be kidding me!
[gasps]
- [roaring]
[rumbling]
So is it dead?
Damn, why didn't that dust work?
Not enough of it?
Needed more firepower?
- [flames crackling]
- [winces]
[gasps]
[dramatic music playing]
Oh, give me a break!
[both gasping]
[mabeasts squeaking]
[Otto moans]
SUBARU: You used
way too much oil!
OTTO: Well, I couldn't
very well be stingy with it!
PETRA: We can't put that out!
We've gotta run for it!
- [sighs]
- SUBARU: Otto.
- [gasping]
- The hidden escape route
in the office
should still be intact.
Get Rem out of here.
- [gasps]
Understood.
I'll take good care of her.
Don't you worry.
- What about you?
- Sorry, but I can't go
with you guys right now.
- [gasps]
- We're gonna have to split up.
- But why?!
- [gasps]
- I'm sorry, Petra, really,
but there's one more person
I've gotta save.
- You mean Miss Beatrice?
- Once I bring her back,
try to be her friend, okay?
'Cause I think
you two would get along.
And she's pretty fun
to tease, too.
- [gasps] Uh-huh.
- I'm counting on you guys!
If I burn to a crisp,
write on my gravestone
the cause of death
was "Otto's oil."
- Oh, no, you don't.
You're not
gonna blame this on me.
Just come back alive,
or I'll throttle you.
- [chuckles]
- Be careful!
Promise you'll stay safe!
[breeze echoing]
EMILIA: Face the disaster
that is yet to come.
[sighs]
[gasps echoing]
- [tones warbling]
- [gasps]
[music playing]
EMILIA: [echoing] I hate you.
I hate you so much.
Since the day we met,
I've done nothing
but despise you.
I can't bear it.
- [gasps]
[panting]
"The disaster
that is yet to come"?
So does that mean
I'm looking into the future now?
[gasps]
[tones warbling]
SUBARU: You're a hero,
as always.
I'm pretty sure
that's all you can be.
REINHARD: Listen, I--
SUBARU: Anyway, thank you
so much for the help!
WILHELM: You cannot
even wield the sword
without it, can you, thief?!
Petra: Subaru, I know you and
Miss Emilia are both tired.
I'm sorry. I just ended up
weighing you down even further.
ROM: My sweet granddaughter
has grown
into such a fine young lady...
- Al: I'm sorry.
- hasn't she?
Al: I'm sorry
I couldn't kill you.
OTTO: ...I should've
just been wrapped up
in that cave and left for dead!
CRUSCH: ...by something
as nonsensical as a curse!
PRISCILLA: There, you see?
It appears I win again.
RAM: To think that somebody
I wanted to kill so badly
turned out to be a kind person.
JULIUS: If I bend my knee
and lose my sword,
what's left for me?
How will that impact
the rest of my life?
- REM: This is a nightmare.
- ANASTASIA: What's so hard
about saying
"I don't wanna be alone"?
GARFIEL: We're not through here!
I'm gonna kill you
just like I promised,
Subaru Natsuki!
ROSWAAL: Oh, nothing, really.
I simply made the realization
that I haven't walked alone
all this time, that's all.
FREDERICA:
I suppose we must shed
every last drop of blood
in our bodies to atone.
FELT: You can just stand there
running in place!
Magic, dragons,
whatever stands in my way...
FELIS: Why won't
the soul take hold?!
FELT: I'll destroy it!
- [shudders]
[gasps]
REM: I believe
praying to ask for a favor
is an act of arrogance.
Prayer should be
for seeking forgiveness.
- [gasps]
[sighs]
[gasps]
[tone warbles]
[breeze blowing]
So, is this...
Echidna?
[sighs]
- You will regret reaching out
your hand so eagerly
for a feast
being offered by a witch.
- [gasps]
- [finger taps]
[sighs]
- Good girl.
Not turning around
is the right choice.
- Wh-Who are you?
I'm, uh, you know...
a witch so terrifying,
it'll give you goose bumps!
- [gasps]
- Where's Echidna?
- About that,
she said that she
doesn't want to see you.
She must have had
a terrible time in the trial.
- I guess so.
By the end of it,
it seemed like
I'd hurt her really badly.
- I see.
How did the third trial
look to you?
I saw a collection
of some very sad worlds.
Were those actually the future?
- They were possible ones, yes.
That being said,
I believe showing you
only the unpleasant options
was most likely
her way of bullying you.
- [grunts]
[chuckles]
You're probably right.
Echidna can definitely be mean.
- You're content with calling
her actions "mean"?
- [chuckles]
- [gasps]
You seem so relaxed.
How can that be?
- Huh?
- Seems weird to me.
I mean, after all,
you saw those awful things
to come, yet you...
- True, but they're
not guaranteed, right?
And even though
they may be possible,
in the end, there's a
chance
things could be
different.
As long as I know that,
it's fine.
Either way,
I can always fight it.
[wind blowing]
- You don't think you'll break?
- If I was alone, then maybe.
But I'm not, and I know
they won't ever leave me.
- It seems you're pretty strong.
Well, that part of you
is nothing like your mother.
- Huh? Hold on.
Are you saying you know my--
[gasps]
- Yes, very well in fact,
but I can't tell you more.
I promised I wouldn't.
- All right, I understand.
I won't ask you
any more about it, then.
- You sure?
- I know what it's like
when you can't say something,
rather than just not wanting to.
Besides...
I've been blessed with another,
and that's Mother Fortuna.
[sentimental music playing]
- I see.
[crying]
I guess her evil plots
do good things sometimes.
- Are you crying?
- [scoffs] Don't be ridiculous!
I don't cry. I don't even
have the right to now.
- Hold on. What do you mean
you don't have--
[gasps]
- What'd I tell you before?
Not turning around
was the right choice.
You're a bad girl.
- [gasping]
- Go straight ahead,
and the trial will be over.
The barrier will be opened, too.
- Hey, witch...
if you see Echidna,
would you mind
telling her something for me?
- What?
- Next time we meet,
let's have a tea party,
a big one with you and
the other witches, if possible.
- [gasps]
[grunts]
All right. I'll be sure
to pass that along, then.
And if she says no,
I'll drag her
by the scruff of her neck!
- [chuckles]
[tone warbles]
[murmurs]
[gasps]
[breeze echoing]
It's open.
[gasps]
[energy humming]
Who's this person?
This should be Echidna's grave,
but somehow it doesn't...
[mysterious music playing]
Incredible. So this is the spell
generating the barrier?
It seems so elaborate.
I don't have
any idea what it's doing.
[gasps]
I think right here.
[no audible dialogue]
[gasps]
[yells]
[music ends]
[breeze echoing]
Huh. Seems like that ended it.
[sighs]
I need to tell all the people
who are waiting for me.
[panting]
Huh?!
[wind howling]
[metal clangs]
[Garfiel growls]
[mabeasts squeaking]
Now what did I tell you?
These mabeasts
don't mean a damn thing.
They're all a piece of cake
for the boss!
- Don't you think you might be
overestimating him a bit?
- [growls]
- [rumble]
- [Garfiel gasps]
- Come on, Rock Piggie!
Get up already!
- Maylie, I was hoping
you'd stay out of my way.
- Elsa?! I don't wanna hear it!
I had to go through
so much work,
because you kept pushing forward
and rushing everything!
Show me a little respect!
- Garf!
So this is where you were!
- Big Sis?! Now what
are you still doing out here?!
Where's Boss and the kid?!
- I've completed
the mission entrusted to me,
and you shouldn't be
the least bit confused
about why I'm here.
- [gasps]
You sisters sure are givin' us
one hell of a hard time!
- Sisters?
Yes, we are sisters.
That only makes things
more interesting, doesn't it?
Two sibling duos face to face.
[claps]
- [snorts]
ELSA: So can I assume this is
a good time for a fresh start?
[Frederica gasps]
- [hissing]
- [squeaking]
- Listen, Garf.
Don't worry about my--
- Hah! They say
the Master Swordsman Reid
laughed as he drew his sword
against a dragon.
ELSA: That expression
describes one who's crazy.
- Yep, and don't you forget it!
[rumbling]
- [screams]
[Rock Piggie groans]
- That's my divine protection
of earth spirits.
Long as my feet
are touchin' the ground,
everything I see
is within my striking range.
- Stay where you are, Maylie,
and don't take
a single step forward.
- Watch, Big Sis,
and keep behind me.
[dramatic music playing]
[Garfiel grunts]
[chorus vocalizing]
[yells]
- [whistles]
- [hissing]
- [gasps]
- Don't worry, Garf!
I'll handle this one!
- [giggles]
- [yells]
- [gasps]
- Rock Piggie!
- [bellows]
- Now come on! Crush him flat!
- [roars]
[roars]
[roaring]
- No. Piggie.
Piggie!
Elsa, do something!
Goodness, what
a little taskmaster you are.
- [groans]
[panting]
- While your body
takes injury after injury,
my wounds will continue
to heal themselves.
Frustrated
by how unfair that is?
- Huh?
I still got
plenty of fight in me!
I'll just keep killin' you
over and over
'til you stay dead.
Ain't that the way, vampire?
- How'd you know?
- Believe it or not,
I've always liked readin' books.
Long time ago, one
of the witches was a vampire.
Now she's dead,
which means you can die, too.
If you swear
you'll never do bad shit again,
I might just
let you off the hook.
- You really are
absolutely precious.
Gusteco, the land to the north
where I was born,
was a very cold
and desolate place.
- Huh?
- I was abandoned as a child.
I hurt people and stole
from them day after day.
I had no time
to think about things
like truly living or happiness.
Once, during a blizzard,
I was stealing from a shop,
and its owner captured me.
- Hey, shut up! Nobody cares!
- Since I was a thieving girl,
he felt justified
in stripping off all my clothes.
But in a frantic search,
I happened to find
a shard of glass.
There was no thought
or hesitation.
I held it tightly
and thrust it into his belly.
After I did, while naked
and shivering in the cold,
I began thinking.
- [growls]
- The blood and the entrails,
they looked so very warm.
If there's happiness
in this world,
it's when you have enough warmth
to make you forget the cold.
It was the first time
I ever knew joy.
But that's lost on you,
isn't it?
- If you knew that,
then why the hell'd
you keep yappin' about it?
- Ah, excellent question.
Maybe it's because
I find you so very endearing.
- Sorry, but there's
already a girl I like.
I ain't got time
for some blood-and-guts-lovin'
psycho bitch!
- How very rude.
But that's okay.
The only part of you
I'm in need of...
are your hot and steamy insides.
- I will kill you,
Elsa Granhiert.
- My love for you will
begin
after your last
breath...
Garfiel Tinzel.
- [yells]
[metal clanging]
[gasps]
- [Maylie screaming]
- [gasps]
- Elsa!
[chorus vocalizing]
- [growls]
- [gasping]
- [snarls]
[gags]
[snarls]
- [grunting]
- [grunts]
- [sighs]
[sighs]
[rumbling]
[Garfiel growls]
[vocalizing ends]
[wind blowing]
What an absolute thrill.
[rumble fades]
- [gasps]
PUCK: You all right?
Being too reckless
can be bad for you, you know.
- There's no need
to be concerned.
Thanks to you, Great Spirit,
I'm now in a position
where at least I can fight.
ROSWAAL: It appears I was
correct to bring you outside.
[both gasp]
- Precautionary,
but with good reason.
I can't have that place,
specifically that magic crystal,
destroyed.
Of course, as you are now,
you should still be able
to achieve your aim.
Will you not attempt to do so?
- Are you proposing I ask
the great spirit to stall you
and use that as an opening?
You must be kidding me.
It's something
I couldn't begin to do,
and even if I tried,
my wish wouldn't be fulfilled.
- Then you must know that things
will only get worse
if we continue.
I admit
you did strike terror in me,
but even a great spirit
is not perfect.
- I've gotta hand it to you.
You're definitely thorough,
aren't you?
When did you
put the spell on Lia?
- Before I headed
to the Sanctuary.
Doctoring the contract
between you and Miss Emilia
while she was
in the throes of depression
after a fight with dear Subaru
was quite simple.
- And your goal in doing this
was to make sure
she stayed discouraged?
- Indeed.
Admittedly,
restricting Subaru's actions
took more effort
than anything else.
He's the last key
to unlocking my dearest wish.
Unlike you,
I'm not merely attempting
to put him through
a series of tests
to see if he's worthy
of my precious daughter.
Don't get full of yourself,
witch's disciple.
- Am I correct in guessing
that you now remember
what happened
before your contract?
- There are plenty of guesses
you could make. Although...
I was actually remembering a man
who spoke a whole lot like you.
Is it so I'd recall
what happened,
a punishment, maybe?
Either way,
you're just stuck in the past.
- I suppose that's true.
Yes. Yes, of course.
I am forever looking longingly
upon my former years,
because, for me, that's when
all the wonderful things
that ever happened took place.
What exists now
is just an impostor
standing atop
a pile of corpses.
PUCK: I'm not going to fault you
for what you are, but...
- Go on.
- You're gonna make
Betty sad, Roswaal.
- Enough. Ul Goa!
- This is how you act
when you're called out?
Childish!
- El Fu--
- Too late.
- [grunts]
- Get back!
If you don't get up now,
the next one'll do you in.
- You make it sound so simple.
ROSWAAL: I couldn't be
more disappointed, Ram.
I wanted you to succeed.
I wanted you
to attain true happiness
by exacting justice
for your brethren.
- [crying]
- Ram?
- After repeating it
over and over,
touching upon it so many times,
you still haven't realized
my true intentions.
I wish I was simply a demon...
one that burns with hatred
in her desire
to avenge her people.
If revenge was
the only thing I sought,
my heart wouldn't torment me so.
[singing in Japanese]
But there's more.
Please listen.
There's something
I need to tell you.
Master Roswaal, I love you.
- [gasps]
- Is something wrong?
- You would seriously
ask me that question,
standing there
and mocking my heart,
after everything
that's happened?
I only told you
what I truly feel.
- Stop lying!
I know that can't be so!
You? You say you love me?
How dare you?! You hate me!
I'm the man who caused
the death of your family
and the destruction
of your homeland!
You loathed me so much,
you wanted to take my life!
- That was true at first,
but not anymore.
What's true now is this.
I love you.
- How could you
possibly love me?
Such cheap emotions
make no sense!
What of your revenge?
Did you not swear
on the souls of your brethren
to achieve it?!
- Yes, and I do feel
as though I've wronged them.
But still,
I can't help caring about you.
My love will be prioritized
over the feelings of the dead.
Now, Great Spirit!
- You got it!
Next to my beloved daughter,
of course,
it's girls in love
that I'll always side with!
- [winces]
[gasps]
Petty tricks.
[yells]
- [shards clattering]
- [gasps]
PUCK: Looking for me?
- It can't be.
[gasps]
- I got you! Surprise!
I just got a little bigger,
that's all!
- [grunts]
[yells]
Hmm?
[sighs]
[gasps]
- [yells]
- What just...
- [scrape]
- [gasps]
- [gags]
- [gasps] How could you?!
- As far as I'm concerned...
this is the root of all evil.
[only song audible]
Now it's done at last.
[song continues]