[wind blowing]
[rumbling]
[wagons rattling]
[animals' steps rumbling]
[Emilia chuckles]
[Subaru gasps]
Hey, Petra...
aren't you a little close?
- Yeah, maybe, but she
had you all to herself earlier,
and I don't think that's fair!
It's my turn.
- Listen, I think you've
got this all wrong, Petra.
Subaru and I were just--
Uh, we had important things
to talk about.
- [groans]
No matter what it takes,
I'm not gonna lose to you.
Understand me?
- [gasps]
- Take it easy, Mili.
She's only a kid.
Just forget about it.
When they say outrageous things,
you've gotta smile
and laugh it off, you know?
- I can't do that!
- [gasps]
- Even if they're
only words from a child,
I refuse to take
such a lackadaisical attitude.
- Who uses words
like "lackadaisical" anymore?
- [growls]
You can't stop teasing me,
can you?
- I'm not a kid,
so don't talk to me like one!
- [both groan]
- Okay, okay, you two.
Take it easy.
Look, I'm sorry, Petra,
and I need to thank you.
You made a promise
not to leave Mili alone,
and you stuck to your word
through thick and thin,
so I really appreciate it.
Once things calm down,
there are actually
a lot of people I need to thank.
I'm grateful
to Crusch and her gang.
Anastasia and her people
helped a lot, too.
I hate to admit it,
but the same goes
for Julius and his crew.
And, you know,
I'm even indebted to Otto.
- Sorry. Were you trying
to say something to me?
- Nah, nothing in particular.
I'm just super grateful
to you, too, buddy!
- [gasps] My goodness.
What brought that on?
You're making me blush.
- Also...
[chuckles]
- What's wrong, Subaru?
- [gasps]
Oh! [laughs] Just, uh--
So listen, Mili.
[sighs]
There's something
extremely important
that I need to tell you.
- Okay. What is it?
- This is gonna be
pretty hard for me to say,
but please hear me out.
And of course
it goes without saying
that I am completely prepared
to be knocked out by Ram
when I tell her!
But I wanted you
to hear it first.
- [grunts]
- This is--
This is actually about Rem.
She--She said that, uh...
- And you'll still
keep me by your side
no matter where you go
from now on?
- S-So you see
what I'm getting at, right?
I mean, well, Rem said
some really nice things
to me, and, uh...
- Easy, Subaru. Just calm down.
Now, I'm not exactly sure
what you're trying to say to me,
but I can tell it means a lot
and you're trying your hardest
to say it, okay?
Just take it slow,
like a good boy.
- "Like a good boy," huh?
Not exactly encouraging.
But all right. Here goes.
[grunts]
Time for me to man up!
Come right out, and say it!
You see...
the thing is,
Rem said that she loves me,
and she meant it in the same way
I told you that I love you!
All right, there! I said it!
[animal's footsteps rumbling]
[gasping]
- Subaru.
- Yes?
- I'm confused.
Who is Rem?
- [gasps]
[shudders]
[indistinct whispering]
- [indistinct singing]
[whispering and singing stop]
[no audible dialogue]
CRUSCH: You don't look
very happy, Rem. What's wrong?
Listen, there's
nothing to worry about.
- I know, but...
- We've got
the best of the best here.
Felix, Wilhelm, and all
of those volunteers are with us.
Ricardo and the Iron Fang
are lending us their aid, too,
so there's no way we can lose.
- Yes, I'm sure you're right.
It's kind of selfish of me
to worry despite all that,
isn't it?
- Just remember
what Subaru Natsuki said.
- [gasps]
- Try to smile,
because you look best
when you're smiling.
- [gasps]
[sighs]
[no audible dialogue]
Honestly...
that Subaru
is such a troublemaker.
[sighs]
Well, I'm sure you'd look
quite different
with a smile, too.
You always carry yourself
with such dignity.
I believe you'd look so lovely
if you'd smile now and then.
- Maybe so.
Unfortunately I'm not very good
at that sort of thing.
It's actually
something I still regret,
even to this very day.
- [giggles]
- [loud rumbling]
- [both gasp]
[shock wave shrieks]
[shrieking continues]
- [shock wave shrieks]
- To arms! Now!
Enemy attack!
[soldiers grunt]
- [chain rattles]
- [grunts]
- Run him over!
[gasps]
[shock wave shrieking]
[shock wave shrieks]
- I wish
you wouldn't have done that.
Why run me over
when I'm not doing anything?
That's not something any
decent human being would try,
if you ask me.
- How dare
you do such a brutal thing
to those brave
and loyal soldiers?
Now tell me,
just who are you, anyway?
- Ah, I see. Things are
becoming much clearer.
You have no idea who I am.
On the other hand,
I know exactly who you are.
You're a candidate
to be the next ruler
of this fair nation.
- Whoever you are,
you talk too much.
Answer my question!
Next time, I will kill you!
- Come on, now.
That's just mean.
But I suppose one could never
hope to properly rule a
country
without some degree
of arrogance.
I can't comprehend
that sensibility myself...
- I warned you!
- but I do recognize its place.
- No second chances!
- Huh?
- [gasps]
Now listen here!
Who taught you
that it was acceptable behavior
to swing a sword at someone
while they're speaking?
I do believe that's a violation
of my right
to freely express myself!
- [gasps]
- [shock wave shrieks]
- [groans]
- Miss Crusch!
[arm squelches]
- [groaning] F-Felix.
- [panting]
- [chuckles]
I keep eating and eating,
but it's never enough!
I eat. I devour.
I chew. I bite. I gorge.
I gnaw. I munch.
I crunch. I savor.
- [metal rattling]
- Pure gluttony!
Ah, thank you for this feast.
I truly appreciate it!
- [gasps]
- [shuddering]
Who are you two? Tell me!
- [scoffs]
- A Sin Archbishop
of the Witch's Cult
representing gluttony.
My name is Lye Batenkaitos.
- And the Sin Archbishop
of the Witch's Cult
representing greed...
Regulus Corneas.
- We came out here, because we
heard our pet had been slain,
and just look at this bounty!
I expected them
to be a good, ripe bunch,
considering they
managed to kill a beast
that had been rampaging
unchecked for over 400 years,
but this exceeds
even my wildest expectations!
Look at this magnificent feast!
Nice! Good!
Great! Excellent!
Fine! Perfect! Fantastic!
Stupendous! Extraordinary!
It's been a while since our
hunger was so thoroughly sated!
- Easy, now. You can relax.
I'm nothing
like that guy over there.
I absolutely despise
fighting and such.
All that hunger
and thirst nonsense,
such petty self-indulgences
are beneath me.
[ice crackles]
Did you listen
to a word I said?
I thought I already told you
I absolutely despise fighting.
- Is that all you have
to say for yourself...
witch cultist?
Soon enough, a hero will appear
and rid the world
of all of you...
the one and only hero,
the one I love.
- Oh? A hero?
I look forward
to that encounter.
And who might you be?
- I am the head maid
of the mansion of Margrave
Roswaal L. Mathers...
the caretaker
of my one and only love,
defender of my beloved
Subaru Natsuki,
who will be that hero someday.
I'm Rem!
[singers vocalizing]
Prepare yourself,
Sin Archbishop!
I promise you
my hero will soon be here...
to take you down!
[yells]
- [yells]
What spirit!
I'm certainly going to enjoy...
this feast!
- [grunting]
- [chuckles]
- [shock wave shrieks]
- [gasps]
- [gobbles]
Yes! Yes!
Thank you for the feast!
[crowd murmuring]
[overlapping chatter, moaning]
[coughing]
- [gasps]
- How awful.
- What happened out here?
- [Felix screams]
- [both gasp]
- [sobbing]
- Wait. Rem.
Hey, where's Rem?! [gasps]
It's just like before.
- Wait a second. Who is Rem?
- But I don't have
a younger sister.
- Rem?
- Just like the time
when the White Whale got her.
But I know for a fact
we defeated that monster,
so why?
[soldiers moaning]
- Rem! Where are you?!
If you can hear me,
say something!
Rem! [gasps]
Rem!
[gasps]
No.
Rem! Rem!
Rem! Where are you?!
Rem! [growls]
Rem! Rem! Rem!
[panting]
Rem...
where in the hell have you gone?
Damn it.
- [chain rattling]
- Huh?
[woman vocalizing]
[gasps]
There you are!
Come on, now! Wake up!
It's me!
Hey, Rem?
Rem. Rem!
- [gasps]
- You know this girl?
- Yes! Her name's Rem!
She's alive, isn't she?
So why isn't she waking up?!
- Unfortunately,
she's beyond help.
There's nothing I can do
to wake her--
- Yeah, and why not?
You call yourself
a healer, right?!
If you are one,
then stop wasting time!
Just wake her up with magic!
Do it!
Now!
Please.
Come on.
[healer sighs]
[fires crackling]
[wind blowing]
- [gulps]
[shudders]
If I Return by Death now...
that means I'll probably
have to go up
against Betelgeuse again.
But I don't care.
I'll fight him
as many times as it takes,
beat him as many times
as it takes.
If that's what I have to do
to save Emilia and Rem,
then I'll do it.
I won't let either of them die.
[shudders]
If it'll save both of you...
then I...
I'll do it!
- [chorus vocalizes]
- [gasping]
[Emilia gasps]
Uh, are you all right?
Subaru, what's the matter?
- [panting]
[wagons rattling]
Where's Rem?
Tell me what happened to her.
- Subaru.
- [gasps]
- I'm confused.
[animals' steps rumbling]
Who is Rem?
[insects chirping]
- Now that I'm
thinking about it,
I've never really
seen you sleeping before.
Every morning, you would
always wake up just before me.
Then the next thing I knew,
you were already
right there in my room,
silently watching me sleep.
Rem...
I am so sorry.
I kept trying
to sound all brave,
saying that I'd die
as many times as it takes.
[sighs] But it just
doesn't seem to matter.
I never make it in time.
[shudders]
- [energy pulsing]
- [gasps]
Oh, hey, Puck. It's only you.
- "Only" me?
That wasn't necessary.
You're so mean.
- It is getting
pretty late, you know.
What brings you
over here, anyway?
- I have a strong connection
with this girl, too, remember?
So what's the matter
with me taking the time
to drop by and check in on her?
- [gasps] Wait a minute.
- Hmm?
- Couldn't you help her out?
- Eh, you'd think so, but sorry.
Not even my power
can do anything to wake her up
from the kind of sleep
that she's in.
- [sighs]
- Now, it might not do much
to make up for that...
- Hmm?
- but I could give you
a little information
about Gluttony if you like.
- And who's that?
- He just so happens
to be the individual
who devoured
her name and memories.
- [gasps]
- To put it simply,
the Authority of Gluttony
is a power for eating.
He can eat someone's name and
make everyone forget about them
or make that person
lose their own memories
by eating them.
If both your name and memories
are taken using this power,
there won't be anything
left of you, but an empty shell,
And that's exactly
what happened to her.
- [shudders]
- Subaru.
- Yeah? What is it?
- I hate to ask a favor of you
when you've already got
so much on your mind, but...
- Eh?
- Take care of Lia for me.
I'm really
counting on you, okay?
[chuckles]
CRUSCH: So this is
where you were. How is she?
- As of right now,
there haven't been any changes.
'Course, it's not as if I
can do something to help.
I know I'm weak and pathetic,
so all I can do is worry.
- No, that's not true at all.
Whether she can show it or not,
I believe your presence
made her quite happy.
- [stammers]
- I'm sorry.
I crossed a line, didn't I?
I've made you upset.
- I'm okay.
Anyway, why'd you
come up here looking for me?
Was there something you needed?
- Yes. Everyone's
gathered in the lounge
to discuss the current state
of affairs, and I was told...
to get, uh...
[sighs]
- It's Subaru Natsuki. Remember?
- I'm sorry. Of course.
You're Subaru Natsuki.
I'm told that I owe you
a great deal,
and yet I've been nothing
but rude. Please forgive
me.
- It's okay.
Don't worry about it,
'cause I'm sure
you must have a lot of things
on your mind right now.
It's not a big deal, really.
Just forget it.
FELIX: I'm sorry for making you
deliver that message,
Miss Crusch!
- No, it's quite all right,
Felix. Thank you, though.
FELIX: Enough with
the formalities!
You and I have
known each other for ages.
It makes me sad
when you talk to me
like you don't
know me very well.
- I'm sorry.
I know it won't be like before,
but I'll try my best.
Is that okay, Felix?
- Oh, absolutely!
There's no need to rush.
Just know that you
can always count on me
to be on your side,
no matter what!
But I must confess,
this is kinda fun!
It feels like I'm seeing
a whole new side of you
now!
- [gasps]
- Are you all right?
- Huh?
Yeah, I'm okay.
I've had some time
to calm down a bit.
I'm fine now. Thank you.
- Well, now that Mr. Subaru
and Miss Crusch have returned,
let us get down to business,
shall we, everyone?
- Then, why don't
we begin by reviewing
where we all currently stand?
By the time the Iron Fang
members who got away
brought back reinforcements
from the capital,
the only ones left were
the casualties and also, uh...
- Those who now find themselves
in situations similar to mine.
- So then,
Crusch's memories were eaten,
and Rem lost both her name
and all of her memories. Damn.
- The capital has also had
many cases of memory loss
that no healer could fix,
like what Miss Crusch's
got,
and an unexplained malady
rendering people
unconscious
that they're calling
the "Sleeping Beauty disease."
But now we know all these things
originated from the same source.
WILHELM: Indeed.
They're the work
of the Witch's Cult.
- [gasps]
- I meant nothing
against you, Miss Crusch,
so please forgive me,
and I must sincerely apologize
for frightening you.
- No, I'm the one
who should apologize
for being
such a hopeless master.
I've been trying my hardest
to remember you as well,
but I'm still having
some difficulty.
- [sighs]
We finally took care of Sloth,
and now there's
another Sin Archbishop
mucking up everything?
I gotta say, this really sucks.
But we all knew from the moment
Miss Emilia became a candidate
in the royal selection,
the Witch's Cult
was sure to get involved.
- So maybe everything
really is my fault after all.
- FELIX: Oh, definitely.
- [Subaru gasps]
FELIX: They're fixated
on getting rid of Emilia,
the one they see
as the half-elf troublemaker.
What's going on now
is just a tiny part
of whatever diabolical--
SUBARU: Stop it!
That's ridiculous!
Try thinking a little more
before you open your mouth!
The only ones at fault here
are those cultist scumbags!
Don't put all the blame
on the wrong person!
Hurting your own allies
with misdirected guilt
won't help anything!
- Huh? That's so much
more convincing
coming from you, Subaru.
I guess it's the difference
in experience?
- CRUSCH: Felix.
- Eh?
- I'm not going to ignore
the comment you just made.
- Oh.
- Apologize now.
- [moans]
- Subaru Natsuki
is absolutely right.
It's crystal clear
where the blame
should fall in this matter.
Understand?
You have no ground to stand on
when you ridicule someone
simply for being correct.
- [whimpers] Of course.
Yes, Miss Crusch.
I apologize, Miss Emilia.
And you as well, Subaru.
- Just forget about it.
Think we should get back
on topic now, okay?
- Sure,
but let me say this first.
- Huh?
- Regarding the alliance
that we were all
speaking of earlier...
can't we just scrap that idea?
- Wait. What do
you mean by that?
How did this discussion somehow
lead to dissolving the alliance?
FELIX: They're only formed
when it benefits
every party involved, right?
Yet you expect us
to align ourselves
with Miss Emilia,
the enemy's target?
Knowing what we know right now,
can you solemnly swear
that Miss Crusch won't be
hurt again if we do that?
- [gasps]
You may have a point.
WILHELM: I'm sorry, but I
am
opposed to that opinion.
- Why would you be against
such a thing, Old Man Wil?!
Look what's happened
to Miss Crusch!
Why should we keep helping
Miss Emilia and her
friends?
I don't see the point!
- Has it yet occurred to you,
with regard to this
Gluttony
who attacked Miss Crusch,
we may be given a chance
to exact our revenge?
- So is vengeance more important
than her actual life?
- I don't think so!
- Felix, please.
- 'Cause I know how difficult
this must be for her.
She has no idea what's going on,
and she can't remember anything,
so how can you possibly
expect her to fight, then?!
I'm only thinking of you
and your best interests.
I'm certain that I can do
something about your memories.
Even if it's
just a little right now,
I'll eventually fix them
completely with my magic!
So please don't put yourself
in any more danger!
- [sighs]
Thank you.
I do appreciate your concern.
At this particular moment,
there's simply too much
I don't understand.
I can't remember a single detail
about just who it was
that I used to be.
I'm sure each of you
must be completely puzzled
as to how you should
interact with me, too.
And for that, to everyone
who still retains their respect
for me despite this,
I must express my thanks.
- Huh?
- Felix, I know
your concern for me is genuine
and that you're trying to
guide me down the safest path.
I could simply do as you wish
and remain out of harm's way,
and nobody here
would think less of me,
but I absolutely loathe
the thought
of going on with my life,
knowing nothing.
If I have a choice
in the matter,
I would rather choose for myself
than simply do as someone says.
- [shudders]
Miss Crusch, I only wanted to...
[crying]
- Thank you, Felix.
- [crying]
- If this is Miss Crusch's will
on the matter,
surely no one favors
dissolving the alliance.
- Yes, that's right.
I know I'll be a great deal
of trouble to you,
so please allow me
to apologize in advance.
- No, really, it's all right.
Though we can't exactly say
we're all
on the same page now, either.
Let's rejoin Ram and those
at the Sanctuary and talk.
We should apprise Roswaal
of this, too.
[Subaru grunts]
[insects chirping]
[sighs]
You once told me I was strong,
but without you,
I just feel so uncertain.
I can't even manage
to find the Subaru
who could put on
that tough guy act. I'm lost.
[door opens]
EMILIA: I knew you'd be here.
- [gasps]
Oh, Emilia.
Did you need something?
- Well, am I not allowed
to be in here if I don't?
After all,
I know this girl, too.
I believe you said
her name was Miss Rem.
- "Miss Rem," huh? Yeah.
- Oh, that's right.
When you were asking me
about her earlier,
I just called her "Rem."
- You got to know her
while being Roswaal's guest.
I don't need to explain
that she's Ram's sister, do I?
- No. I can tell.
She looks just like her.
There's no mistaking that.
Subaru, you haven't slept,
have you?
Maybe you should rest
for a while.
- Maybe. I've got no reason
to be tired, though.
What can I do, anyway?
- Look, I can tell you want to
do something about all of this.
If your spirit is
desperately trying to help,
after a while, the stress will
eventually wear your body out,
so please, rest.
- [chuckles]
Man, I am so pathetic.
What a joke.
- No, that's not true,
because you've helped me
so much, Subaru,
and in so many ways.
I really mean it.
Everything will be just fine.
Not that I have any right
to talk like I'm certain,
but I want to understand,
to know how you feel,
though I don't remember
this girl at all.
And that makes me think,
whatever I say would only end up
hurting you, instead of helping.
Either way, please let me
tell you something.
I want you to know
you don't have to carry
this burden all by yourself,
so let me share it.
Whatever you need,
I'm here to help.
- But, Emilia...
why, though?
You already told me you don't
remember anything about her.
- Is it wrong to want to help
simply because
I don't remember her?
She's obviously
important enough to you
that what happened to her
is making you miserable, right?
So then, is it really so strange
that it makes me want
to help her, too?
- [gasps]
- You saved me, remember?
I want the opportunity
to save you this time.
If you're in pain,
I want to help you.
I want to do something!
- You're amazing, Mili.
You know that?
- I am? I think
you're much more amazing
than I could ever be.
- No, I'm really not.
I'm glad it was you.
- [gasps]
- [chuckles]
Hey, Emilia, I have
a small favor to ask of you.
Sure. What is it?
- Could you please
turn around for me?
I'm gonna cry.
- [sighs] Yes, of course.
- [crying]
[gasps]
I swear I'll get you back.
I promise you.
I will get you back.
Your hero
is going to come for you!
I give you my word!
Just wait for me...
Rem.