[HAYAMA] Do you want
some rolled omelet?
[YOKO]
Oh, no.
Thank you very
much for offering,
but I couldn't, really.
I am so sick and tired of that
smug little teacher's pet!
Sorry. We haven't met before.
Are you a friend of Hayama's?
[STUDENT 2A]
Okay, everyone. It's lunchtime!
See you all back here
after the break.
[STUDENT 2B]
So what'd you bring for lunch?
[STUDENT 2C]
I'm buying today, actually.
[STUDENT 2D]
Let's hurry. I'm starving!
[YOKO]
My name is Yoko Nishikawa,
and I come from
a wealthy family.
Unfortunately, my father's
company fell on hard times.
It went bankrupt, and now I have
to live like an ordinary girl.
But it might not be
as bad as I thought.
The other day, something
wonderful happened.
I made two new friends!
[HAYAMA] Hey. Do you want
some rolled omelet?
[YOKO]
Oh... No.
Thank you very
much for offering,
but I couldn't, really.
Come on. Just have some.
But if I do that, there
will be less left for you.
[HAYAMA]
Don't worry about it.
[YOKO] No, it's your lunch.
I really can't.
[HAYAMA]
Sure you can.
[YOKO]
No, I can't.
--[FUTABA] That's enough!
--[HAYAMA] Yes, you can.
[FUTABA]
This is ridiculous!
You're being so polite you'd
think you'd never met before!
Can't we all just relax?
Sure. What'd you have in mind?
Well...
For starters, we could come up
with nicknames for each other.
That's the kinda
thing friends do.
Oh, that's right.
We are friends.
[HAYAMA] Are we really
good enough friends
for nicknames, though?
[FUTABA]
That's a good point.
Nah, maybe not.
It's way too early
[HAYAMA laughs]
It's okay, Yoko,
we're just teasing. Sorry!
[rustling]
Uh, something wrong?
[CAT meows]
Hey, a cat.
I suppose it must be a stray.
[HAYAMA squealing]
You all right?
[CAT meows]
[HAYAMA]
Can't breathe! It's too cute!
[HAYAMA] What's the matter,
widdle kitty?
Is poor widdle kitty wost?
[laughs]
You're so cute!
I don't think I've ever seen
her enjoy herself like this.
Freaky, isn't it?
She's kinda got
a thing for cats.
Actually, I love cats,
dogs, cows, horses,
bunnies, and even
little birdies, too.
My dream is to gather up
as many animals as I can find
and open Hayama Park,
my island sanctuary!
[YOKO]
What an amazing idea!
It's almost like
she has a heart!
[HAYAMA] Well, at least
I have a brain, piggy.
I had no idea you
liked animals so much.
Do you have any pets at home?
[HAYAMA] Yeah. We have a sweet
little kitty cat named Bel.
How nice!
He's the most adorable
thing in the whole world.
Bel is short for
Mister Beelzebub.
Is that so?
[YOKO]
"Beelzebub! A prince of demons.
Also known as Lord of the Flies.
A demon who takes
the form of a fly!"
That's her pet?!
The poor little baby was
just swarming with flies
when we took him in.
That's where he got his name.
[TEACHER 2A] Hayama,
can I borrow you a minute?
Oh, yes, of course.
If you make sure
that everyone gets
one of these before
next class, that'd be great.
[HAYAMA]
Okay.
[TEACHER 2A] Can you also
collect homework during break?
Everyone should have
a notebook to turn in.
[FUTABA]
Man, that's a lot of worksheets!
[YOKO]
What was I thinking?
I must have been crazy!
Hayama is such a good student.
Obviously she's no demon!
It seems like it
must be awfully difficult
to be the class representative.
There's a lot to do.
Honestly, I didn't
want to take the job.
The teachers insisted,
though, so...
But if you didn't want to,
couldn't you have refused?
Mm... Well, even though
I kinda hate doing
all the extra work all the time,
It's gonna look amazing
on my resume, so here I am!
[YOKO]
Huh...
[FUTABA laughs]
[STUDENTS chattering]
[STUDENT 2F]
I studied really hard, too.
[STUDENT 2L]
There's always next time, right?
Hey look at that!
You're tenth in our grade.
Great job!
So what's Hayama's rank?
[NISHIYAMA]
Ah! Stop!
Don't say it!
I don't wanna hear it!
[KONDO]
It's all right!
Grades aren't everything.
There's much more
to you than that!
Look on the bright side!
You're ranked a lot higher
than you were in middle school!
What really matters
is you're improving!
I am so sick and tired of
that smug little teacher's pet
always getting in my way.
I can't take it anymore!
I wanted to be class rep, but
of course they gave it to her!
Yeah, that was harsh.
You wanted it so much.
[NISHIYAMA] I mean, why did
they choose her, anyway?
Just because she looks the part?
[FUTABA]
Yeah.
I'm sure it's not because
she's smart and responsible.
[NISHIYAMA]
Huh?!
It's her!
[NISHIYAMA whining]
Is this girl
a friend of yours?
Well, Hayama had a
little chat with her once.
It was kinda brutal.
She said being
class representative
was going to my head!
It hurt my feelings!
[HAYAMA crying]
[STUDENT 2G]
What's going on?
[STUDENT 2I]
What's wrong with Hayama?
[STUDENT 2H]
Poor thing's crying.
[STUDENT 2M]
Is she getting bullied?
[NISHIYAMA]
You won't get away with this!
[KONDO] Wow, people say
that in real life?
Oh! I need a moment.
That was scary!
The girl's got skills.
Perhaps she is
a demon, after all.
[TEACHER 2B] All right, now that
we've gone over the equation,
let's test your ability
to apply it.
Todoroki, come to the board
and try the first problem.
[TODOROKI]
Okay.
[P.E. TEACHER 2A]
Push it! Come on!
Get those legs moving, ladies!
Ugh, I hate these timed runs!
Can't we just have
a snack instead?
[FUTABA] Look at Hayama!
She's doing really well!
[FUTABA] Wait, no she's not.
I'm gonna lap her.
[P.E. TEACHER 2A]
C'mon, move!
Run like you mean it, or I'll
have you doing laps all day!
[HAYAMA]
Don't say anything.
You can't talk
back to a teacher.
Just keep it all inside.
[FUTABA whines]
[HAYAMA pants]
I'm gonna die!
[FUTABA]
Hey, are you okay?
[HAYAMA]
How could I be? She's evil!
She was trying to
run us to death!
[NISHIYAMA]
How the mighty have fallen.
Even the great Hayama
has a weakness, huh?
[HAYAMA]
Nishiyama.
Quit being a jerk.
[HAYAMA]
It's okay. Don't mind her.
The poor little thing
only looks down on people
to make herself feel better.
She deserves our pity
more than our anger.
I don't need anybody's pity!
Of course you don't!
You're not little!
You've got a great figure.
It's nothing to be ashamed of.
[NISHIYAMA] Why are we
talking about my figure?
But, well...
I do think it's important to
take care of your body.
A balanced diet and proper
exercise can do wonders.
[NISHIYAMA]
Booyah!
[HAYAMA]
That must be tough.
You have to watch what you
eat and work out all the time
to maintain your weight?
I thought that only
happened to old people.
[NISHIYAMA]
That's not it!
That's not what I was saying!
Why do you always
twist my words?
[HAYAMA]
What? I don't do that!
She does have skills.
[STUDENT 2K]
Bye!
[STUDENT 2J]
See you tomorrow!
[HAYAMA] I still feel
like I'm gonna vomit.
[YOKO] You really don't
like running, do you?
I just don't have the stamina
to go on and on like that.
Ugh, I don't think I
could run another step.
Is something wrong?
So much for not
running another step!
[KITTENS meow]
[YOKO] Were they abandoned?
Whaddaya think we should do?
[HAYAMA]
I can't believe it.
Look at how tiny
and helpless they are.
It's terrible.
How could anybody
abandon them like this?
[YOKO]
She may hide it,
but Hayama actually has
a kind and gentle spirit.
[HAYAMA]
"Please take care of us"?
Oh, really?
I'm gonna take care of whoever
abandoned these poor kitties!
I'll take care of them so well,
they'll wish they
had never been born!
[HAYAMA laughing]
[YOKO, FUTABA]
Yup, she's a demon.
[HAYAMA] I was able to find
homes for two of them.
That leaves one more, though.
Well, it won't be easy,
but maybe I can take it.
But I'll have to move somewhere
that allows pets first.
Slow down, now!
Ugh. I can't be the only person
at this school who loves cats.
[KONDO]
Did you say cats?
[HAYAMA]
Yes, I did.
[KONDO] I don't know
if it helps, but Nishiyama
used to have a cat.
[NISHIYAMA]
A cat?
I don't know why you care,
but yes I had one.
It passed away
about three years ago.
[KONDO]
Your family had that cat since
before you were born, right?
You must've really loved it.
I don't wanna talk
about it anymore, okay?
[HAYAMA]
Oh, Nishiyama!
I never, ever thought
I would say this,
but you're actually
good for something!
If you were aiming for
a compliment, you missed!
[NISHIYAMA]
Welcome to your new home.
[NISHIYAMA gasps]
I can't believe
I agreed to this.
[NISHIYAMA] Well, it's not
like I had much of a choice.
And this has nothing
to do with Hayama.
It's only for the kitten's sake.
[KITTEN meows]
[NISHIYAMA gasps]
We need to find a
name for you, huh?
[NISHIYAMA] You're gonna be
around a long time, I know it.
All right, girls.
Let's get down to business!
[BOTH]
Huh?
Ugh! We have to
come up with nicknames
for each other, remember?
It slipped my mind.
Yes, I remember.
It's something we need to do!
What are we waiting for?
We can't be real friends until
we have nicknames, right?
I'm not exactly sure
that's how it works.
I humbly ask this favor.
As a sign of our friendship,
will you please
give me a nickname?
[HAYAMA, FUTABA]
Well, uh...
Loco Yoko!
Purple Princess!
[YOKO]
Not approved!
[FUTABA]
What, you don't like either one?
[YOKO]
Ugh! No, no, no, no, no!
They are entirely unacceptable!
You should be striving for
something noble, intellectual,
something that connotes beauty,
grace, and magnanimity!
[HAYAMA, FUTABA]
Uh...
--Former Rich Chick!
--Purple Princess!
[YOKO growls]
Did you even hear me?!
[YAMAJI] Please address
Miss Yoko as "Miss Yoko."
[FUTABA] Hey, look who's popping
out of the bushes again!
[HAYAMA] You appeared so
suddenly without making a sound.
I thought you were
a stalker or something!
[YAMAJI]
A stalker? Me?
But anyway, the only name
that truly fits Miss Yoko
is "Miss Yoko."
[YOKO]
Wha--?!
Yeah, that's a great idea.
Sure!
What do you say, Miss Yoko?
Like your new nickname?
Well, I had thought my nickname
would be something different,
not the name I've
always been called by.
So, that's settled.
Yoko is officially
Miss Yoko now.
You're next, Hayama.
[FUTABA]
Wait a sec!
I don't actually
know your first name.
[FUTABA] I mean, mine's
Futaba, hers is Yoko.
But yours is some big
mystery for some reason.
[HAYAMA]
Isn't this nice?
If you ask me, there's nothing
like a picnic on a sunny day!
[FUTABA]
Aw, c'mon. It's only fair.
You know our first names;
you should tell us yours!
Seriously, stop stonewalling
and tell us already!
Anyway, what are you
doing after school?
Uh, I'm not really sure--
Ugh! Out with it!
I don't understand why
you're making such a big deal
out of this.
--Just tell us your first name!
--[KOU] Hey, Teru!
I've been looking all over!
Teru?
Who's that?
That's your name?!
[YOKO, FUTABA gasp]
There, you know.
Are you happy?
Teru. Terry? Ter-Bear?
Stop that right now!
Hey, relax.
It's really cute, huh?
Absolutely.
I think it's quite lovely.
We'll come up with a
great nickname for you!
[HAYAMA]
Leave me alone!
I forgot to pack chopsticks
with my lunch this morning,
and I don't know
what to do about it.
[HAYAMA] I'm sure they
have disposable ones
in the cafeteria.
Oh. Yeah, you're right!
I knew you were
the person to ask!
Thanks a lot.
I'd be totally lost without you.
Sorry. We haven't met before.
Are you a friend of Hayama's?
Actually I'm more
than just a friend.
I'm Teru's older sister!
Her sister?!
Are you for real?
[YOKO] Is it truly possible
they're related?
A demon and an angel.
You know April Fool's Day
has come and gone, don't ya?
Just drop it.
Well, anyway,
it's nice to meet you.
Like I said, I'm
Teru's older sister.
My name's Kou.
Oh, yes, hello!
It's a pleasure to meet you.
[KOU] Hold on a second,
are you Yoko?
I am.
[KOU]
Ha, I knew it!
Wait here and
I'll be right back!
Where's she going?
[KOU] Here, take one.
I made them from scratch!
No...
--That's so nice, thank you.
--[FUTABA] Ooh! Candy!
[KOU]
Would you like to try one, too?
Oh, okay!
Down the hatch!
What happened to her?
[KOU] This candy really packs
a punch of nutrients!
It's made from fermented beans!
[YOKO]
Okay...
Please take one.
A girl can't live on bread
crusts alone, ya know?
I know my sister.
She seems sweet, but she's
not always the nicest person.
I hope you'll stay friends
with her anyway.
[YOKO]
What?
Never mind what she says.
She has a pretty bad habit
of running her mouth
before her brain gets involved.
Kind of a ditz, but harmless.
What's a ditz?
Hey, look at the time!
If you don't hurry up, you won't
get to eat any lunch at all!
[KOU]
Well, see you later!
The candies were good,
but I think they can
be better, don't you?
Maybe I'll try a different
recipe next time.
[HAYAMA]
Whatever you want.
[BEELZEBUB meows]
[HAYAMA] Come on, Bel,
it's still really early.
I should get to sleep
in a little bit.
That's what weekends are for.
[BEELZEBUB meows]
[HAYAMA cooing]
[HAYAMA gasps]
Where'd you come from?
Time to get up, sleepy head!
Wow, you're chipper.
[KOU] Are you excited
about breakfast?
You should be!
I'm gonna make a
smoothie for you!
That's okay.
[KOU] This morning's
secret ingredients
are garlic and banana!
[chuckles]
I think I'm gonna
sleep a little more.
[KOU]
Aww.
Well in that case,
I'll see if Bel wants to try
some of my
super-special smoothie.
Wait, I'm up!
[HAYAMA groans]
So gross. More than gross.
It's just plain wrong.
[KOU]
Hey, Teru.
I'm going shopping today.
Do ya wanna come with me?
Well?
[KOU]
This is nice, isn't it?
It's been awhile since
we've gone out together.
[HAYAMA]
Sure has.
So, what all do we need to get?
[KOU]
Just a few things.
I need some books.
[HAYAMA]
What kind?
I thought I would try
to find a good cookbook.
And I'd love a photo album!
Anything else?
[FUTABA]
Hayama! Hey!
Wow, look! It's Futaba!
Are you girls just out
having a sister-bonding day?
Yep. We haven't spent nearly
enough time together lately,
so I dragged her out with me.
Man, I'm jealous.
I always wanted a sister,
but I'm an only child.
[HAYAMA] At least no one's
trying to poison you.
You getting your weekend
shopping done, too?
I'm gonna pick up
some giblets.
Ooh! That gives me an idea!
Wha--?!
The grocery store's
right over there, let's go!
[HAYAMA] Hey, hold on.
Is that really necessary?
[KOU]
Here, you see...
We'll have giblets, Chinese yam,
okra, and mulukhiyah
all mixed together.
This is gonna be
my best candy yet!
[FUTABA]
Blegh.
Why the obsession with
making health foods into candy?
Doesn't that kinda
defeat the purpose?
That's the only way
some people would try it.
[CUSTOMERS shouting]
[ANNOUNCER 2A] Today only,
we're having a special sale
on mayonnaise!
That's right!
We're knocking 50%
off the regular price!
Cheap mayonnaise?
[ANNOUNCER 2A]
You don't want to miss out!
Hurry, while supplies last!
[YOKO]
Against all odds, I succeeded.
I've acquired my very own
bottle of discount mayonnaise!
[laughing]
[HAYAMA, FUTABA]
How embarrassing!
[YOKO]
What a coincidence!
Out of every store in the city,
I can't believe I ended up
running into you ladies.
Are you sure you
want to give me
all of these raffle
tickets, though?
Yeah, don't worry
about it, we have plenty.
Have you seen the prizes?
Fifth place gets tissues,
fourth, a coffee set!
It's really not that exciting.
Third place is a bag of rice!
Not you, too...
Whoop-di-doo,
a bunch of tissues.
I love my brand
new coffee set!
[FUTABA groans]
Check it!
[FUTABA]
That's a huge bag of rice!
I just can't believe I won!
Ack! The only thing
I really wanted,
and the "demon"
gets to take it home?
[bell ringing]
[RAFFLE MAN 2A] Congratulations
to our big winner!
[KOU] Can someone give me
a hand with all this?
[YOKO, FUTABA]
No way!
[HAYAMA]
This happens a lot.
She has pretty good luck
with this sort of thing.
I'd call that more
than pretty good!
She's also the one who got
us those bathhouse tickets.
[YOKO]
Oh, that was her?
Please! I can't
carry it all myself!
[KOU]
I'm exhausted!
It was really nice of Yoko and
Futaba to take the heavy things.
I'll give the hot springs
vacation to Mom and Dad.
They'll love it!
[gasps]
What is it?
I totally forgot to
go to the bookstore!
Why even bother
buying a cookbook?
It's not like you're gonna
follow the recipes, anyway.
[KOU] Yeah, but I wish
I'd got a photo album.
[HAYAMA]
Why do you need that?
Well, I was looking
through the closet,
and I found a bunch
of old pictures.
They brought back
so many memories
from when we were little.
[HAYAMA]
Be careful up there!
Please don't fall, okay?
Don't worry so much!
You know I'm a
real good climber!
[KOU]
A little further. Almost there!
I've just gotta
catch this butterfly.
Teru's gonna love it!
[KOU screams]
That was kinda dumb
Oh, no! Are you okay?
[KOU]
I don't know if you remember,
but when we were younger,
you used to get sick
and hurt really easily.
[HAYAMA]
Yeah, I know.
I'm pretty healthy now, though.
But you should still
take care of yourself,
and make sure you're getting
lots of vitamins and minerals.
[HAYAMA]
Is that it?
Is that why she's always going
on and on about nutrients?
[KOU]
It's fine!
I'll try to make something
nutritious, and tasty!
[HAYAMA]
Because she's worried about me?
Thanks a lot, Sis.
[HAYAMA]
Kou made these as thanks
for helping us out yesterday.
[KOU]
Homemade rice balls!
Stuffed with liver, white roe,
and bitter melon.
Really?
But what about all the
stuff you bought yesterday?
I'm all about staying healthy,
but this is taking things
a little too far!
[YOKO] I'm sure Hayama's
sister put in a lot of time
and effort into
making these for us.
We owe it to her
to at least eat one.
Here goes!
[FUTABA]
Oh my gosh!
[HAYAMA]
She's choking it down!
[FUTABA] Thanks for taking
one for the team, Yoko!
How could you allow
Miss Yoko to ingest
such a vile thing?!
Uh... You really
don't have to eat it!
Although I gotta admit, your
dedication is very impressive.
[HAYAMA] Stop that!
Don't encourage her!
[YOKO choking]
[KOU] Well, maybe they're
right when they say
nothing good for you is tasty!
[FUTABA]
This must be great for you!
[HAYAMA]
Don't encourage her, either!
[YAMAJI]
Miss Yoko!
[YOKO] Being rich is
not all that wonderful.
But that does not mean
my current life is great.
[FUTABA] You wouldn't
be green after eating
a strange rice ball, either.
[YOKO, FUTABA] But, all of us
being able to eat the rice balls
that Hayama's sister
made for us...
[HAYAMA]
...makes us happy.
[FUTABA] Your real
thoughts are leaking out.
[YAMAJI]
Miss Yoko!