[HAYAMA]
Why is Nishiyama here?
[NISHIYAMA]
Why is Hayama here?
[NISHIYAMA] Are those tears?
Hayama's crying?
[YOKO]
That was strange.
She's all alone.
I wonder what's going on.
[SHINO]
Here!
[NISHIYAMA cooing, giggling]
Now, now. Let's all
play nice, okay?
I've got plenty of
love for everybody.
Nishiyama, your drink's
ready whenever you are.
Oh, thanks!
Kono's gotten
so big, hasn't she?
[laughs] She's quite the
little troublemaker now.
[door opens]
Welcome to Tricky Cat!
Is a counter seat all right?
[KOU]
Sure!
Hey, sleepyhead! You awake?
I've got a surprise for you!
[HAYAMA yawns]
[KOU giggling]
[KOU] I found a shop I
think you're gonna like.
It should be just up ahead.
Yeah? What kind
of place is it?
Oh, you'll see.
I think it's absolutely
perfect for you.
Come on, let's go in!
No! I can't!
I would be cheating on Bel!
It's cruel to
tempt me like that!
Relax. We'll just hang
out for a little bit.
You know you want to.
[HAYAMA]
Here. Might as well use this.
So you were already
planning to come here.
I heard about it a while ago.
I wish you had told me this
was where we were going.
I couldn't.
I wanted it to be
a surprise for you.
[HAYAMA]
I don't have my camera,
so I'll have to use my
potato of a cellphone.
Poor baby!
[HAYAMA]
Why is Nishiyama here?
[NISHIYAMA]
Why is Hayama here?
[HAYAMA] This was supposed to
be a special experience.
She's going to ruin it!
Look! It's your friend.
The one we saw at the beach.
Oh, hello.
Nice to see you again.
That's Nishiyama.
And she's just a classmate.
Hey!
Weren't you one of the people
who helped Teru out before?
You adopted one of
the abandoned kittens
that she found, right?
Uh, yeah?
That's so sweet!
So what did you
end up naming her?
Oh. I guess I forgot to ask.
Gimme a break. Like you care.
We named ours
Little Beelzebub.
You know, like the
lord of the flies,
'cause the poor thing
was swarming with them
when we found it.
It's Bel for short, though.
I wanted my little one
to have a name
that reflects my undying love,
so I decided to call her
Eternal. She's "El" for short.
--[HAYAMA giggles]
--[NISHIYAMA] What?!
Nothing. That's a
very creative name.
Yep. I can just imagine you
pouring through a thesaurus.
[KOU]
Hey, Teru.
Have you heard the names of all
the kitties they've got here?
Princess Konohana Sakuya,
Lakshmi, Viracocha,
and Teutates.
Well, that's a little much.
I like their names.
I think they're
refined and regal.
Or ridiculous.
Think about it for a sec.
Do you wanna be out in public
talking about your cat
"Princess Konohana Sakuya"?
Well, you can think
whatever you want.
It's not like I came here
to talk to you anyway.
I've got better things to do.
Like play with
sweet little kitties!
[SHOP WORKER]
Hey Nishiyama!
It's good to see you again.
How are you?
Good, thank you.
I'm really glad
to see Mi here today.
I've missed her.
She wasn't around
the last time I came,
so I was getting worried.
[SHOP WORKER]
It's so sweet of you to worry.
Listen to that.
It sounds like she's kind
of a regular around here.
[HAYAMA] I'm not jealous.
Not even a little bit!
[FUTABA]
Oh, yeah?
That's kinda random.
I mean, running
into her like that.
It isn't that surprising.
[HAYAMA] Hmm... I wonder
how I could convince her
to send me those pictures.
[FUTABA]
I have something for you,
but if you've already gotten
your fix at the cat café...
[HAYAMA]
What is it?
A ticket to Animal Town.
Y'know, that petting zoo place?
[HAYAMA]
What?!
Give it to me!
I'll do anything!
[FUTABA]
Okay, calm down. It's yours.
Sakura's mom actually
gave it to me.
I figured you'd appreciate
it a lot more than I would.
[HAYAMA]
This is awesome! Thanks!
Oh, hey, it says it's
good for two people.
So when do you
think we should go?
Huh? Looks like it's
good till Sunday.
We'll have to buy one ticket,
since there are three of us.
I wasn't gonna go.
I don't like animals
all that much.
What?!
I can't go either. I'm working.
[HAYAMA]
Really? You too?
Hey, maybe you could
bring your sister along.
I dunno about that.
Yay! Let's have some fun!
Are you ready, Teru?
Sis, calm down.
Aw! Who's a little cutie?
You have to be gentler
with the little ones!
This one is adorable!
Aw! And so is that one!
Take a deep breath.
Slow down and adore
them one at a time!
Going with Kou would
be too exhausting.
I'd have to protect all
the animals from her.
Hey! I know!
[NISHIYAMA]
Animal Town?
[FUTABA]
Yeah.
Yoko and I can't go, but we
thought you might want to.
What do ya say?
Me? Really?
Hold on!
What are you doing?
I don't wanna go with her!
Well, I think she'd like it.
Don't you?
Besides, you went to
the cat café together.
[HAYAMA] We definitely
did not go there together!
[NISHIYAMA] I have a feeling
this isn't going to end well.
Morning.
Back at ya!
[FUTABA] Nishiyama showed!
I can't believe it.
I thought Hayama had
scared her off for sure.
Their love for animals
must be stronger
than their hatred for each other
You came too?
Checking up on them?
[KONDO] Well, yeah.
You know how they are.
They're going in!
I gotta see how this ends.
Welcome to Animal Town!
[FUTABA groans]
This is gonna be a
long day, isn't it?
[NISHIYAMA]
Hey sweetie! Look over here!
[NISHIYAMA squeals]
You pups have a very
important job, don't you?
Yes! You're the first thing
people see when they walk in.
Thank you for
all your hard work.
You're doing great!
[KONDO] They've been
at it for ten minutes.
When are they gonna move on?
[FUTABA]
I don't know, but at this rate,
Nishiyama's going
to run out of memory.
[NISHIYAMA]
Just because we came in together
doesn't mean we
have to stay together.
I don't see any reason
why we can't split up.
[NISHIYAMA]
All right.
The small animals are closest,
so I'll go there first.
Then the dog show.
After that, the cat room,
the small dog petting corner,
the exotic animal show,
and the horse park.
Well, see ya later.
We're probably better off
going our own ways.
Sure, fine by me.
[NISHIYAMA]
No way!
Did she plan out
the same route I did?
[STAFF]
Jump and catch! Good boy!
Let's give Jack
a hand, everyone!
Wow! Good boy!
[NISHIYAMA] Are those tears?
Hayama's crying?
I don't know why
so many people
have children when
they could have dogs.
A puppy is just as cute.
In fact, I'd say
that they're cuter!
I think that's taking it a
little too far, don't you?
So I guess they decided
to stick together after all.
Think they'll be okay?
Things could get violent.
Well, Hayama will
behave herself.
She won't start a fight.
How do you know that?
Because she made a vow
to exercise self-discipline.
What does that mean?
She said she wants
to open herself up
to new experiences by being
more tolerant of others.
And I think there was
something about inner peace.
Okay, sure.
I'll pretend that makes sense.
Still...
If Nishiyama deliberately
provokes her,
I don't know what could happen.
She might crack.
[NISHIYAMA]
Over here, little cutie!
Wow, Nishiyama.
You're really good at that.
You've got them hooked.
Yeah.
I thought it was something
that came naturally
to all cat owners,
but I guess you must not have
the knack for it, though.
You know,
you're probably right.
I should practice!
[NISHIYAMA]
What did you get to drink?
It looks like juice.
I decided to get tea instead.
I don't think juice is healthy
because of all the sugar in it.
Oh, wow!
You're being so good!
I wish I had that
much discipline.
[NISHIYAMA]
That one there?
It's a Weimaraner,
also known as the "Gray Ghost"
because of the color
of its coat.
You mean you seriously
didn't know that?
That's really amazing!
Is there anything you
don't know about animals?
I am fairly knowledgeable.
[NISHIYAMA] I don't get it.
She's being so nice today.
I've never seen her like this.
It's almost like somebody else
has taken over her body.
Jeez!
Nishiyama's not holding
anything back, is she?
The dam is gonna break
any second now.
[KONDO]
Ah! Can't she see it?
[laughing]
Today's going a lot better
than I thought it would.
Being around you isn't
as painful as usual.
It's almost fun.
Nishiyama?
Yeah? What?
Something wrong?
[HAYAMA laughing]
[NISHIYAMA screams]
[NISHIYAMA crying]
[NISHIYAMA]
What is Hayama's problem?
She seemed totally
normal all day,
and then out of nowhere,
she said those awful things!
I hate her!
[NISHIYAMA]
Did you come to cheer me up?
[meows]
You're so sweet.
Thank you, El!
[YOKO] Did you have
fun at Animal Town?
It was a lot of fun, actually.
I want to go back sometime.
And spending the day
with Nishiyama?
How did things go
between the two of you?
You know, same as usual.
About halfway through the day,
she got angry for
some reason and left.
It seemed like she
was having a good time,
and there was still
a lot left to do.
Maybe she got upset because
I said her desperate need
to seem superior was the
funniest thing I'd ever seen.
[FUTABA] It's hopeless.
They'll never get along.
[YOKO]
Like cats and dogs.
[FUTABA]
Well, I tried. It's too bad.
I really thought it
might end up working.
That what would work?
You know, how I fixed
it so that Hayama
and Nishiyama went
to Animal Town together.
I thought it would be
a good chance for them
to bond or at least get
to know each other better.
Aw, that's sweet.
Actually, it was
self-preservation.
Class is getting pretty
awkward with those two
always at each other's throats.
Oh...
Why can't you just get along?
You've got so much in common;
it should be easy.
You know, it's funny...
That sounds a lot like something
I said to you recently.
Finished the
Mega Ogre Rice Omelet.
What's for dessert?
[SHOP OWNER]
That's it. Time's up!
Spoon down please.
[HAJIME]
Aww...
I lost again.
She beat me!
Don't think that you've
heard the last of me yet,
Futaba Odagiri!
I won't forget this!
[sobbing]
[SHOP OWNER]
Thanks for coming!
Can't you get along?
You have so much in common.
Nope. Not a chance.
[FUTABA]
Hayama!
[imitating guitar]
Let's start a band!
And why would we do that?
'Cause it's the
season of the arts.
[YOKO]
What are you two doing?
[FUTABA]
Hey! We're starting a band.
You wanna join?
You two look like
you'd be musical.
Our band is gonna rule!
What?
[HAYAMA]
What now?
♪ River of Three Crossings. ♪
♪ But I cannot find a way
to reach the other side. ♪
[YOKO] I didn't realize
your sister could sing.
Her voice is almost hypnotic.
♪ I close my eyes
and dream. ♪
I feel dizzy.
Anybody else's ears
hurting, or is it just me?
[KOU (SONG)]
♪ River of Three Crossings. ♪
♪ But I have no coin to give. ♪
I want to pick
that flower up there.
Yamaji. I need you
to be my ladder.
Wee!
[KOU (SONG)]
♪ River of Three Crossings. ♪
--♪ River of Two Crossings. ♪
--[YOKO] Go get it, Yu! Hurry!
[KOU (SONG)]
♪ River of One Crossing. ♪
♪ River of No Crossings." ♪
♪ River of sadness
and days forever lost. ♪
♪ La, la, la, la,
la, laaaa, la." ♪
[HAYAMA]
Yoko!
[FUTABA]
What's going on?
Wake up!
Thank goodness you're back!
You had me really worried
for a second there.
What happened to you?
Did you pass out or something?
[YOKO]
That was strange.
Were those memories?
Thank you.
That was "River of Three
Crossings," sung by Kou Hayama.
[FUTABA]
So depressing!
Why sing about the river people
cross to reach the afterlife?
[KOU]
Oh, come on.
Haven't you ever
just started singing
without thinking about it?
I do it all the time.
Like when I'm cooking
or doing chores.
Nishiyama, you know
what I mean.
You sing songs
dedicated to Eternal
when you're alone in
your room, don't you?
No way! I don't do that!
Ooh! I wanna hear one!
Sing one for us, please!
I'm telling you,
there aren't any songs!
Nishiyama! Nishiyama!
Stop it! People are
starting to stare.
[KONDO] Nishiyama! Nishiyama,
yeah! Nishiyama, whoo!
Nishiyama, hey! Nishiyama, go!
Nishiyama got
so mad yesterday,
I thought she was
gonna punch someone.
Yeah, I kinda felt bad for her.
After what you said
to her at Animal Town,
I find that pretty
hard to believe.
Hey, look.
Do you see that?
[FUTABA]
Yeah. It's Kondo.
I don't think I've ever
see her all by herself.
She's usually glued
to Nishiyama's side.
[YOKO] She's all alone.
I wonder what's going on.
Did she and Nishiyama
get into a fight
because of what
happened yesterday?
She's been abandoned
by her best friend.
It breaks my heart!
[HAYAMA] But you always
eat bread for lunch.
[FUTABA] I've told you before,
rice is my favorite food.
[KONDO]
Seriously? Rice?
Oh, Kondo.
Yep.
She's gonna have lunch with us
today if that's okay with you.
She was walking around
like a lost little puppy.
So I figured I'd invite her.
What a wonderful idea!
A jerk who would
abandon you like that
doesn't deserve your friendship!
Don't worry.
We'll be your friends now!
What?
[FUTABA] Do you think
maybe she's being
a little too welcoming?
[HAYAMA] Miss Yoko does know a
thing or two about being alone.
Nishiyama's my best friend,
and she's not a jerk.
She's actually really nice.
Once you get to
know her, anyway.
She just has a
very fragile ego.
Well, anyway,
why don't we eat?
Sound good?
[FUTABA]
Elementary school, huh?
So you two have known
each other a long time.
[KONDO]
Mm-hmm.
Since the third grade.
We ended up in the same
group during a field trip.
She was our group leader.
Whenever she saw me
starting to fall behind,
she would come to help me.
So you're saying
she's always liked
being the one in charge.
Yeah, pretty much.
I gotta admit...
She wasn't always as
difficult as she is now.
It's high school, right?
You gotta learn
to go with the flow.
Plus, these days there's always
somebody getting in her way.
Oh, dear. Do you mean me?
[laughing]
[FUTABA] If Nishiyama
could just be more careful
about what she says out loud,
I bet she and Hayama
could actually get along.
They have so much in common.
You could teach her a lot.
I bet she could even be class
representative someday.
But that's only if she
could pretend to be nice
the way that you do.
Uh...
You could work on
that too, actually.
You come off so
prickly and snobby.
Try talking to the people
in your class sometime.
Huh?!
The problem is
you're too pretty.
So it's your job to
start conversations.
Really? You think I'm pretty?
Yeah, totally!
If a pretty girl...
[FUTABA]
What the heck's going on?
[HAYAMA]
Is she being nice?
Being mean?
Or just plain oblivious?
Basically, you should
try harder to talk to people.
[YOKO]
Right. Okay.
[KONDO]
Thanks a lot for today.
Sure, no problem.
[SASAME]
Futaba Odagiri!
You beat my brother at
a food challenge again,
didn't you?
[huffing]
To be fair, I didn't actually
know we were competing.
And you get to eat lunch with
Nishikawa every single day!
Just the three of you,
like some little clique!
I don't know
what to tell you.
I guess I'm just special.
Special? Special?!
[SASAME yells]
She's an interesting one, huh?
Well, you're pretty
interesting yourself, Kondo.
[FUTABA] Ramen's best with
pork, tons of veggies,
and a nice, runny egg.
Am I right, or am I right?
[laughs]
Hey.
I was hoping you would
come with me somewhere
if you're not busy.
[door opens]
Hello. Wait, I know her.
You're never too old
for cosplaying, right?
Yes, how could I forget?
Nishiyama's friend
who has no tact.
Perhaps you can help us.
Kondo wants to pick out
something special
for Nishiyama to
help them make up.
What do you mean "make up"?
Yes. I have just the thing!
[SHINO]
Here!
[YOKO]
Why did you bring that out?
[SHINO]
It's something Nishiyama likes.
[KONDO]
Hey! I recognize that!
It's the uniform Nishiyama
wore when she worked here.
A cake, Sonobe!
We want a cake she likes!
[KONDO laughs]
I gotta say, that was
really funny, though!
I'm so glad I was
able to amuse you.
Is it really true that
you used to be a servant
and you worked for
Nishikawa's family?
[SHINO]
It is.
So she was a
rich girl once,
just like everybody's
always saying.
That explains a lot
about her personality.
Like how overbearing
and stand-offish she is.
She really has no
filter, does she?
Hope she doesn't
try that with me.
[YOKO] I think this is
really big of you, Kondo.
[KONDO]
Huh? What do you mean?
She's the one who
should apologize
for blowing things
out of proportion,
and yet here you are,
going out of your way
to heal the rift between you.
Uh...
Uh, Yoko...
I'm sorry, but I think you
misunderstood what's going on.
[HAYAMA] Kondo wasn't alone
because she and Nishiyama
got into a fight or anything.
Nishiyama's sick.
So she had to stay home
from school today.
What?!
I... I just--
Well... I just assumed.
[KONDO]
Here. Take a look.
I sent her a ton of
emails this morning
to see how she was doing.
[YOKO]
No!
But all the things I've said!
I feel like an idiot!
It's all right.
These things happen.
Don't worry about it.
It's kinda your fault, too.
You weren't all that clear
about the situation, so...
[NISHIYAMA]
What's the deal with her?
Why did she suddenly stop
emailing me after lunch?
She sent so many this
morning I couldn't sleep.
[EL meows]
[meows]
My sweet little girl.
You always know when I need you.
♪ Eternal is your name, love. ♪
♪ One that means
so much to me. ♪
♪ E-T-E-R-N-A-L. ♪
[FUTABA]
Kou was right.
She's singing a song
dedicated to her cat!
We finally get to hear it!
Do you think we should
go in or come back later?
Let's listen until she's done.
It's beautiful.
--What?!
--Huh?!
[NISHIYAMA (SONG)] ♪ R because
you're really cute. ♪
♪ N because you'll never leave.
A for... ♪
[KONDO]
It's Asako...
[NISHIYAMA] ...and Selina's
preview for the next episode.
[NISHIYAMA] I've had enough!
Just do whatever!
[KONDO]
Oh, really?
Then, why don't you sing a
character song or something?
[NISHIYAMA]
What?
[KONDO] Character song!
Character song!
[NISHIYAMA]
I... I guess I have no choice.