Can either of you
think of the kind of job
that I might be qualified for?
Let's ask Yamaji.
I bet he'll have some ideas.
[YOKO] I could be wrong,
but I think it's blood.
[ALL scream]
[SHOP OWNER 3A]
Thank you. Come again soon!
[WOMAN 3A]
Oh, good morning, Yamaji.
Just making sure
Yoko's doors are secure?
Oh... yeah.
Is your back
still bothering you?
Lemme help with that.
[FUTABA, HAYAMA]
Miss Yoko!
--Good morning!
--Wait for us!
Hold on a second!
Hello, you two.
Come on! Let's walk together.
It's perfect weather
for a picnic today.
It is lovely out, isn't it?
[HAYAMA]
I don't know for how long.
I heard there's
a typhoon coming.
[ALL gasp]
[YAMAJI]
That wind...
Something about it
makes me uneasy.
[HAYAMA]
This is nice.
Much better than that awful
weather we had last week.
Yes, it was terrible, wasn't it?
But I'm glad we're able
to eat outside again!
[FUTABA sighs]
Is something wrong?
This is usually your
favorite time of day.
[YOKO]
That's strange.
You brought your own lunch?
Don't you prefer to buy it?
Yep, but I burned
through my lunch allowance
for the month already, so
this is what I'm stuck with.
[YOKO]
What did you spend it on?
Well I developed a
pretty expensive habit.
I got hooked on sea urchin.
Oh.
They say all it takes
is just a little taste.
[FUTABA]
Man! Being broke is the worst.
Maybe I should get
a job or something.
[gasps] Like where you do manual
labor in exchange for money?
[HAYAMA]
Well, that's the gist.
I wonder what kind of
job would be best for me.
I could work at a cake shop.
Or maybe a bakery.
Or a café! That could be nice.
Are you hoping that
they're going to pay you
with money or with food?
Either will work, really.
I'm not picky.
[YOKO]
That gives me an idea!
Instead of being destitute,
I may have to consider
getting a job myself!
Can either of you
think of the kind of job
that I might be qualified for?
Huh...
Miss Yoko wants to work?
How would that go?
[YOKO]
Here's your menu.
Don't take too long deciding.
Excuse me!
Who do you think you are,
ordering me around like that?
Do I look like a servant to you?
If you want coffee so
badly, refill it yourself!
Not so good.
Not good at all. Nope.
Oh! Hey, I know!
Let's ask Yamaji.
I bet he'll have some ideas.
Hello?
Shouldn't he pop out of his
stalker hiding place about now?
"My poor Miss Yoko!" Right?
[grunts]
[YOKO]
Futaba?
What is this?
[FUTABA] Wow!
Did we get lucky or what?
I've heard about this place.
It hasn't been open that long,
but I've really been
wanting to try it out.
An adorable little cake shop.
Doesn't that sound perfect?
I mean, really!
What could be better
than this, you guys?
I'm gonna have my
cake and eat it too!
You know it's a job,
not a buffet.
I'm not so sure about this.
Maybe you two should
go on without me.
You want a job, don't you?
This is your chance.
And we'll be with you,
so don't worry.
[FUTABA]
What a cute little shop!
Ah! So yummy!
Oh, wow. I haven't
had cake in so long!
Excuse me! Is anyone here?
[HAYAMA]
What is that?
I could be wrong,
but I think it's blood.
Ah! I was afraid
you would say that!
Looks like it leads
into the hallway.
I don't see anybody in here.
Let's just go back!
[YOKO] The trail disappears
behind this door.
[ALL scream]
[YOKO]
This is simply horrific!
[HAYAMA]
Is that a real body?
[FUTABA whimpering]
Wait a moment.
I think her hand just moved!
It's a zombie invasion!
[screaming]
Whoops. That was
very careless of me.
[HAYAMA]
Uh...
I had a severe
craving for sweets,
and I thought this berry
jam would be just the thing
to satisfy it.
I must've fallen asleep
while eating again.
You were sleeping?
Standing up with
your eyes wide open?
It really is you, Sonobe!
But what in the world
are you doing here?
Oh. Hello, Miss Yoko.
It's been a while, hasn't it?
Wait, you know each other?
[YOKO]
Yes.
She worked for my family
before, well, you know.
My name is Shino Sonobe.
I used to be the
Nishikawa family's maid.
[HAYAMA, FUTABA]
Seriously?
[SHINO]
I enjoy making sweets.
In fact, it's one of the
few things I'm good at.
Losing my maid position
gave me a new opportunity.
I was able to further
my abilities as a baker
and open my very own shop.
[YOKO]
That's excellent!
You know, I don't think I've
ever met a real maid before.
So you went from
working for them
to owning your own business?
I don't believe we
have been introduced.
I'd like you to meet
my two new friends!
I'm Hayama.
Nice to meet you.
I'm Futaba.
Sonobe?
Uh, what's the matter?
I'm sorry, that was
just quite a shock.
It seems like everyone
who knows "Miss Yoko"
is surprised that
she has friends.
You've got a funny way
of showing you're surprised.
The idea of working
at a place owned by
someone you know must
make you feel better.
[YOKO]
It certainly does!
You're suggesting Miss Yoko
would work at my shop?
[YOKO]
Yes! That is...
...if you think I'm qualified
for the position, of course.
Oh, absolutely.
In fact, Miss Yoko,
I'm counting on you!
[gasps]
[YOKO]
Somebody is counting on me!
[echoes]
[FUTABA]
Don't forget me!
I want a job here, too!
[SHINO]
Oh, yes!
I'd be happy to hire you!
A friend of Miss Yoko's
would be very amu--
I mean, very dependable.
Are you here for a job, too?
Me? No, I'm good. But thank you.
What was that?
Milk bottle caps?
What do you think
you're doing, Sonobe?
[ALL]
Yamaji!
Good. Our milk delivery is here.
You can just put it all
in the refrigerator.
[YAMAJI]
Don't change the subject.
You haven't answered
my question.
Miss Yoko isn't like us.
She can't have a job!
My stomach hurts
just thinking about it.
Okay...
[HAYAMA] I'm a little
worried too, actually.
I'm already having
a hard enough time
arranging my schedule so
I can keep an eye on her!
I don't need you
complicating things!
[SHINO]
By the way, Mitsugu,
thanks for helping me
find this property.
It's perfect.
[YOKO] You helped her
get this shop set up?
Yeah.
I had a job at a real
estate agency, and--
Never mind!
You can't possibly force
Miss Yoko to work here!
I want her to!
Besides, Sonobe says
she's counting on me!
Don't do it.
No disrespect, but you don't
know that you're getting into.
[YAMAJI grunts]
Careful, you might accidentally
hurt somebody, Sonobe.
I was only swatting at a fly.
I understand.
It seems there are a
lot of flies around here!
[yelling]
Stop this despicable
display this instant!
Put those utensils down
and behave yourselves,
do you hear me?
[FUTABA] Jeez. That was
kinda scary, wasn't it?
It doesn't seem like the most
nurturing work environment.
I'm terribly sorry you had
to see them act so shamefully.
Maybe we should
try looking around
for a different place to work.
And who knows,
there might be other ways
for you to make money
besides working.
[SHOP OWNER 3A]
Thank you. Come again soon!
Ah! Now that's what
I'm talkin' about!
[FUTABA] I ate a mountain of
dumplings and got paid for it.
What could be better?
Maybe I'll make it
through this month
without getting a job after all.
[HAYAMA]
I figured you could do it,
but I had no idea
it would be that easy.
[YOKO] I have to admit,
I'm a little jealous.
I've been thinking about it,
and there's nothing
I'm particularly good at.
Come on!
I'm sure that's not true.
Yeah, don't beat
yourself up so much.
There are plenty of
things that you're good at.
Do you know what kind of job
would be right for
somebody like me?
Yeah.
Well, uh...
[giggling]
You could work as a waitress.
At a themed restaurant!
What's that?
[HAYAMA] You know, a place
where the servers all act
a certain way.
Like a cafe where the
waitresses are really snobby.
[FUTABA] Is that a thing?
Do they really have those?
[HAYAMA]
I'm sure they do somewhere.
Guys like weird stuff.
[YOKO]
Hold on... I'm snobby?
[FUTABA]
Really, I mean it.
You make the best dumplings!
[SHOP OWNER 3A]
Thank you. Come again soon!
[HAYAMA]
I shouldn't be surprised.
Oh, hey, Hayama!
[HAYAMA]
You'll bankrupt that poor man.
[FUTABA laughs]
Nobody's forcing him
to offer prize money.
All right!
Now I'm gonna take this
and buy something yummy!
You're still hungry?
Ooh! I know where to go.
How 'bout the maid's place?
Our last experience
there wasn't the best.
But I'm not gonna lie...
The cakes she gave us
were pretty good.
[FUTABA]
They were more than good!
How can I describe it?
It was like having
a taste of maid!
I don't even know
what that means.
[HAYAMA, FUTABA]
Hello!
Welcome to Secret Garden!
[BOTH gasp]
Oh, hi!
I didn't expect to
see you here today.
[HAYAMA]
Wha--
You're not wearing
a maid outfit?
That's what you ask?
It's not a uniform.
I just like wearing it.
[FUTABA, HAYAMA gasp]
[YOKO] It seemed far
less daunting for me
to work for somebody
who I already know.
And when I found out Yamaji
would be working here, too,
I knew I would feel
right at home!
[FUTABA]
Of course he is.
[HAYAMA] I wonder how
his stomach is doing.
I think it's great
you got a job here.
Working for a friend
sounds like a lot of fun!
Sonobe seems really young
to own her own business.
I guess she must be
some kind of prodigy.
What is she, 18?
I don't blame you for thinking
that, given her appearance.
But you're way off the mark!
In fact, I think she's
in her early thirties.
[HAYAMA, FUTABA]
You're kidding!
Excuse me.
[ALL gasp]
There seems to be an
empty spot at the table,
so I'll join you.
[HAYAMA]
So, anyway...
Hey, is it true you're
really in your thirties?
Getting a job is
a big step for Yoko.
Is she doing well here?
Yes.
Since it's a small shop,
the menu wasn't
too difficult to learn.
The customers are very friendly.
And the food is delicious!
I suppose I should go
and check on things.
I'll be back out soon.
She's actually a good worker!
I gotta admit I'm
pretty impressed.
Not everybody gets the
opportunity to hire someone
who once hired them.
You have no idea what a
thrilling experience it is.
[YOKO] The look on their
faces when they walked in!
I wonder what they
thought when they saw me.
I bet they were surprised!
Well, it was nice
to see you again.
We should be going.
Please...
You're welcome to stay
as long as you would like.
Don't rush on my account.
I have some freshly baked
treats if you're interested.
[HAYAMA]
Oh... sure.
Yeah! I'll take two!
[SHINO] The presence of young
people is invigorating.
I feel as if I
can eat so much more.
Like it vicariously
raises my metabolism.
Yeah? That's cool!
[HAYAMA]
Um, she's joking, right?
Because that's the
most ridiculous thing
I've ever heard.
[YAMAJI]
Oh.
I guess I shouldn't be
surprised to find you here.
[FUTABA]
Oh, hey!
Yeah, we've kinda been hanging
out for a little while.
What, have you been
hiding somewhere?
No.
I only come in the morning
to help bake the first cakes
of the day.
I'm not here all the time.
Ah, that explains it.
Well, I just stopped by to
see how things were going.
Miss Yoko? Are you all right?
May I be of any assistance?
Another job?
He must be one of
those crazy workaholics.
He's exactly the same as always.
Shows up without any warning,
gets everything done,
and then moves on
to the next place.
Yeah, that sounds
just like him all right.
Just between us, I honestly
can't stand people like that.
They make me sick to my stomach.
[HAYAMA]
Uh...
[SHINO] But anyway, tell
me about high school life.
It must be fun. Is it fun?
Kinda. Lunch is fun, anyway.
That's what I look forward to.
But mainly, we're all
going there to learn.
[SHINO]
Fascinating.
Miss Yoko.
Since you've worked
so hard today,
you can end your
shift a bit early.
Really?
Mitsugu is still here
if I need help.
I'm not really here.
I just work in the mornings.
Oh, cool! We can walk
home together, then.
Yeah!
[YOKO sighs]
It's surprising how
exhausted you can get
just from standing.
You're doing a whole lot
more than just standing,
aren't you?
Is it weird to serve customers
after being waited on
your whole life?
[YOKO]
Uh...
Well, it's difficult,
but I manage somehow.
Why, did you think I would
yell at them or something?
[FUTABA, HAYAMA laugh]
[FUTABA] So you're raking
in the big bucks now.
What are you gonna spend it on?
[HAYAMA] Maybe you can eliminate
bread crusts from your diet.
[YOKO]
Why would I want to do that?
They're cheap and plentiful.
Not to mention delicious
when topped with mayonnaise.
[FUTABA, HAYAMA]
Of course.
I'll be seeing you
ladies again very soon.
Aww... I'm gonna
starve to death.
One more class to go
before lunch, so you'll live.
[SHINO]
Futaba! Hayama! Futaba!
Is somebody calling us?
Wait, that voice.
I know it from somewhere.
[SHINO] Turn around. I'm
standing right behind you.
Do you think I could borrow a
moment of your time, please?
[BOTH yell]
[HAYAMA]
Wha--Wha--Wha...?!
[FUTABA] What in the
world are you doing here?
[SHINO giggles]
Oops. Did I startle you?
That isn't the problem!
Now, where did you get that?
[SHINO]
Oh, this?
I made it after
you left yesterday.
It wasn't too difficult, really.
The pattern itself is
a very simplistic one.
[HAYAMA]
You know, never mind.
I think I asked
the wrong question.
Start by telling us
what you're doing here!
[FUTABA]
That's right!
And why aren't you
wearing the maid outfit?
You're really not helping!
I change clothes
sometimes, you know.
[HAYAMA]
Can we focus, please?
This is what I would
like to know.
What are you doing
at our school?
I don't mean any harm.
I'm simply trying
to be of service.
What, fan service?
[FUTABA] That would work
better with the maid getup.
Can we drop that already?
Well, anyway, there's something
I want to give Miss Yoko.
Oh? And what would that be?
[SHINO] I went overboard
with my prep today.
I thought she might enjoy it,
so I boxed some of the
extra food up for her.
Ooh, you made her lunch?
[SHINO]
There, you see.
I have a perfectly good
explanation for being here.
[chuckling]
Nope. There's just
no good explanation
for a woman in her thirties
trying to masquerade
as a high school student.
[bell rings]
There goes the bell.
We should get to class.
Well, Sonobe,
what are you going to--
[FUTABA]
Hey! She disappeared!
[HAYAMA]
She's a poltergeist.
Since I have to wait until
lunchtime to give this to her,
I guess I'll just explore
the school until then.
[SHINO]
The feel of a linoleum floor!
Ah!
The scent of youth!
So, so, delicious!
Ah, what a lovely view!
[SHINO]
I love being up this high!
It's so empowering!
And school uniforms
are perfectly designed
to catch this breeze.
[TEACHER 3A] The subjunctive
mood is easily identified
by the use of a clause
beginning in "if."
It is used to express...
[SHINO yelling]
Um, is it just me,
or does it sound like
the school's being
attacked by Tarzan?
It's the poltergeist.
[P.E. TEACHER 2A] All right!
Everybody pair off!
Get those stretches done!
Come on!
Stop all the chit-chat!
[HAYAMA]
I don't know what to do.
Well, first things first,
we need to find Sonobe--
'Kay, found her!
[SHINO] So it appears that
you are schoolmates,
but not actually classmates
with Miss Yoko.
[FUTABA]
Uh...
I don't understand
why you're here.
I wanted to eat
lunch with you,
so I made a uniform
and came to your school.
[HAYAMA]
Which is crazy, right?
[FUTABA] Yoko doesn't
seem too fazed by it.
When one works with Sonobe,
one accepts that
strange things happen.
[HAYAMA, FUTABA]
Yeah?
[SHINO]
There's plenty.
Help yourselves to
whatever you want.
Sounds great!
Don't mind if I do!
[SHINO]
I made potato salad,
with a generous amount
of mayonnaise, naturally.
[YOKO] You do know
what I like, Sonobe.
[HAYAMA]
'Kay, you handed over her lunch.
Maybe you can
just get going now.
It was so nice of you
to think of me!
[SHINO]
Here you are, Miss Yoko.
It's from your father.
[YOKO laughs]
Aww!
Did you draw these
cute little pictures?
Yes.
I thought the letter
would be more enjoyable
if it were illustrated.
Thanks!
That's very sweet of you!
[FUTABA]
Careful, Hayama.
You want to make sure
you're having balanced meals!
[HAYAMA]
Give me a break!
Like you're one to talk!
I don't know what you mean.
I eat plenty of bread, rice,
meat, and veggies every day!
[HAYAMA] Sure, but you're
not supposed to eat
truckloads of 'em!
[FUTABA gasps]
I don't eat that much!
Thank you for your time.
I need to get back to
the shop, so I'm going now.
You're going already?
[SHINO] Hayama, Futaba,
I leave Miss Yoko to you.
Please take good care of her.
Sonobe...
[YAMAJI]
What is the meaning of this?!
[YOKO]
Yamaji?
How dare you!
Prancing about in a uniform.
[SHINO laughing]
[YAMAJI]
Get back here!
[ALL]
Uh...
I wasn't sure at first,
but I think she came here
because she was
worried about you.
Yeah, I think so too.
She's pretty weird, but she
seems like a good person.
[YOKO]
Yes, she is.
[SHINO]
Here you go. Here you go.
Here you go. Please take one.
Here you go.
Delicious cakes.
New specials every day!
Please, take a flier with you.
[YOKO]
Sonobe?
[SHINO]
Miss Yoko.
Would you mind
telling me what exactly
you think you're doing out here?
Oh, I'm sorry.
Would you like one too?
[YOKO] No, I wouldn't!
That's not the issue!
[FUTABA]
Easy now.
[HAYAMA] Maybe you should
take a deep breath.
[YOKO] You really think
it's okay to be doing this?
Yes, absolutely.
I'm quite confident
that nobody can tell.
[YOKO]
Can tell what?
That you're a grown woman
hanging out at a high school?
[SHINO]
No, this uniform is perfect.
[YOKO]
That isn't the issue either.
Wait! Come back!
Hold on! Sonobe!
[SHINO]
This is Maid Angel Super Shino!
I'm so happy you enjoyed this!
From this week on, I'll be here
to put a smile on your faces!
Please support me!
You will, right?
I will fight
with what I have!
Perish! Unpaid overtime!
Illegal uploading!
[YAMAJI]
What year are you in?
[SHINO]
2016.