I will be the wife of a CEO.
The most loyal dog ever!
Who are you talking about?
You'd have more luck with
a single-lens reflex camera
and a telephoto lens.
Good to see you, Sis!
Hi! It's nice to meet you.
My name is Sakura Usada.
[YOKO]
Yamaji? Yamaji?
[YAMAJI]
You called, Miss Yoko?
How may I be of service?
[YOKO] I've invited some of my
classmates to visit tomorrow.
We shall be playing
in the garden.
[YAMAJI]
What a wonderful idea!
Begin preparations at once.
Your wish is always
my command, Miss Yoko.
[YOKO laughs]
I'm simply delighted
you could be here!
If it's agreeable to you,
I thought we might play house.
Yes, that sounds delightful.
Indeed!
I will be the wife of a CEO.
I will be the wife
of a top lawyer.
And I will be the wife
of a real estate tycoon.
I'm crazed today!
I have a massage
and a mani-pedi,
and Snookums must get
to the groomer for a trim.
I still can't decide
between foie gras or shrimp
for tonight's dinner party!
Now ladies, take care not
to work yourselves too hard!
[laughing]
And that's just one of
the many adorable moments
from Miss Yoko's
childhood I still cherish.
If you keep this up,
you're going to embarrass me!
Were you literally
born with a silver spoon
in your mouth?
It doesn't sound like
you two have changed much.
I'm curious...
Was Sonobe weird back then, too?
[HAYAMA] You didn't say
anything about her.
[YAMAJI] Honestly, she hasn't
changed that much either.
What about you?
What were you like
when you were little?
When I was a kid...
Hi, Mom! I'm home!
You have fun at school?
Sure! What's for snack?
How about some
nice white bread?
Sounds good!
--[FUTABA'S MOM laughs]
--[FUTABA] Yummy!
[FUTABA]
I was pretty energetic.
Always playing or eating.
[HAYAMA]
Sounds about right.
It's your turn, Hayama!
Oh, do I have to?
[HAYAMA crying]
[KOU] Aww, what's the matter?
Why are you crying?
[HAYAMA]
Santa doesn't like me!
He brought me the wrong present!
[KOU]
I'm sure that's not true.
What's wrong with it?
I told him I
wanted a white tiger,
and this is what he gave me!
This stupid pink cat!
I even gave him options!
I said that my second
choice was a puma,
my third choice
was a snow leopard,
and my fourth choice
was a saber-tooth tiger!
Well, Mr. Santa obviously
isn't doing his job
'cause you deserve to
have whatever you want!
[KOU]
Cheer up, Teru.
There's always next year!
[HAYAMA]
I know, but...
...what if it's my fault
things turned out this way?
[HAYAMA] Santa didn't
get me what I wanted
because I was a bad girl.
I have to be good from now on.
I'll study hard
and say nice things.
I'll be a perfect student.
No one has to know
I'm pretending.
Especially Santa.
That's when the demon
within you awakened!
I don't know what you mean.
I think it's sweet
how your sister
has always looked out for you.
Man, it must be awesome
to have a big sister.
I'm super jealous.
[KOU]
Um, hello?
[HAYAMA]
And there she is.
I wanted to join
you all for lunch,
but you practically need
a map to find this place!
We're actually done eating,
but we can stick around
a little longer.
[KOU]
Anyone want some bitter melon?
[FUTABA]
Ooh! Like in a stir-fry?
Nope, just raw. Yum!
[HAYAMA, FUTABA, YOKO]
Ugh!
So you still jealous?
Hey! Tomorrow's the big day.
Are you excited?
A big day?
Uh-huh!
Well, in the cat world.
[NISHIYAMA]
You've gotta be kidding me!
My kitty is so much
cuter than any of these.
Its coat is silkier.
Its eyes are prettier.
Anyone can see it's just
more adorable in every way!
Wait!
[KONDO]
Hey, good morning!
Hello? Earth to Nishiyama!
What magazine are you reading?
Something wrong?
[NISHIYAMA]
I'm so sick of this!
How does she always beat me?!
[HAYAMA]
You should calm down.
None of these kitties deserve
that kind of treatment.
Is that what Kou
was talking about?
[HAYAMA chuckling]
You mean the picture of
my pwecious widdle kitty cat?
[meows]
Which one is it?
There are so many of them,
and they all
kinda look the same.
[HAYAMA]
What?!
He's obviously the most
beautiful one of all!
Are you blind?
[FUTABA] Yeah, he's a
special little snowflake.
[NISHIYAMA]
So it's true.
That really was your
cat's picture I saw.
I'll admit he is a cute one.
Mine's still much cuter, though.
[KITTEN meows]
Yes, the kitten you got
from me is adorable.
But let's be honest
with each other.
Mine is by far the
cuter of the two.
[BOTH growling]
[NISHIYAMA]
Yeah, you're right.
Little Bel is pretty cute.
[HAYAMA]
Aw, so is yours!
Just look at that sweet face!
[NISHIYAMA]
Here, kitty.
[HAYAMA]
Here, kitty, kitty, kitty.
Aw kitty, kitty,
kitty, kitty, kitty.
Ugh! Cat people!
[giggling]
Congratulations, Hayama.
Your cat is really adorable!
I wish I could have a pet.
Living on my own
might not be so lonely
if I had a little friend
to keep me company.
But my apartment
doesn't allow it.
Then maybe you
should move someplace
that will let you have one.
I don't have the
means to relocate.
Well, you do kind
of have a pet already.
The most loyal dog ever!
Who are you talking about?
Oh, you shouldn't
compare Yamaji to a dog!
That's terrible. He's my friend.
Do me a favor.
What?
Take this stick and
throw it over there.
Then say "fetch."
Just trust me.
[YOKO]
Fetch!
--[YAMAJI] Here.
--[GIRLS gasp]
You're seriously creepy,
you know that?!
No, I'm not!
[NISHIYAMA]
I'll show her.
I can do it too!
It can't be that hard.
[NISHIYAMA] I'll take the most
squee-inducing picture
in the history of cat magazines!
[KITTEN meows]
Now that's cute!
Hey! Come back!
One shot!
That's all I need. Just one!
Will you just hold still?!
[KITTEN meows]
[NISHIYAMA growls]
Everything okay?
[NISHIYAMA]
I have a newfound respect
for animal photographers.
[HAYAMA]
You need better gear.
You'd have more luck with
a single-lens reflex camera
and a telephoto lens.
Oh, yeah?
You're not really
gonna buy that stuff?
You don't really own
that stuff, do you?
I guess owning
all that stuff means
photography's your hobby?
Oh, no. More of a duty,
really. Really.
[FUTABA]
Geez!
There must be something
you do for fun, right?
I dunno, I keep pretty
busy most of the time.
I do enjoy reading.
Like what, international
guides to torture?
Actually, I finished
reading most of those
in middle school.
Right. How silly of me.
What about you, Futaba?
Is eating your hobby?
[FUTABA]
How can eating be a hobby?
I eat to survive,
just like everybody else.
[HAYAMA]
Yeah, sure. Hmm...
Would you please stop
staring at me like that?!
So if eating enough
to feed a small army
isn't your hobby, what is?
I don't eat that much!
You're just being mean!
What is my hobby, though?
I really like to cook.
Can you stop playing
around for one second
and give us a straight answer?
I told you mine.
What?
You know reheating
food's not cooking.
Neither's opening a package
or making a sandwich.
I know what cooking is,
thank you very much!
I like to eat,
so I like to cook!
I don't see why that concept is
so hard for you to understand!
[HAYAMA]
Just tell us your real hobby!
Do you listen when I talk?
If I have something
good at a restaurant,
I wanna recreate the experience,
so I'll try to make
it myself at home.
So it is more
about eating, then.
Fine, why don't we just say
that eating out is my hobby?!
Well, in that case...
If you two don't mind
I have a small request.
[YOKO] I've wanted to see
what this place was like
for a long time.
I would wistfully imagine
dropping by with friends
on the way home from school.
Now I'm here!
It's not exactly
five-star dining,
but they make good fries.
It popped into my
head when Futaba said
her hobby was eating out.
I thought we could grab a bite.
Let's get this party started!
[YOKO]
Oh! Just look at it!
This is exactly the
meal I've dreamed of!
Way to dream big there, Yoko!
But to complete
the experience,
we must talk endlessly
about vague and silly things
whilst we eat.
Go ahead!
I'm not really sure
what you want me to say.
I've nothing
particular in mind.
The usual chatter regarding
animals and food
should be just fine if you--
Those are not vague
and silly things!
Everything you
hoped it would be?
Actually, I can't
help but feel like
there's something missing.
But I'm sure a little
dollop of mayonnaise
would make it much better.
Should we be concerned
about your mayo habit?
Um, I have a question.
This might not be
the right place,
and it's not about
something silly.
But I feel like we've
gotten to know each other
well enough that I can ask.
This sounds serious.
I was just wondering
why you're living alone.
What are your parents doing?
I can't answer that.
My mother has been
gone a long time.
She passed away
when I was quite young.
As for my father...
[HAYAMA]
What about him?
[YOKO] After he lost everything,
he didn't give up.
He decided that he
was going to start over.
He came to me and said...
"Don't worry, dear.
It'll be all right.
Daddy's gonna do something big!"
I don't know where he is
now or what he's doing,
but he sends money regularly,
so I'm sure he must
be working hard.
You've had a pretty
rough go of it lately, huh?
Hence the bread
crusts and mayo.
[FUTABA] This must be
a huge change for you.
Yes.
If you ever need anything,
feel free to ask us.
We're here to help.
That's the whole point
of having friends.
[YOKO]
This was amazing!
Thank you for making
my dream come true.
[HAYAMA]
It was no big deal.
I'm happy to hang out
any time you want,
just lemme know.
As long as it's something
involving food, right?
[YU]
Is that you, Yoko?
Wow, I was right!
Good to see you, Sis!
Did he just call you "Sis"?
You never mentioned having
a little brother before.
Uh, I don't.
He's not my brother.
My name is Yu Takezono,
and Yoko and I
aren't related by blood.
We're promised to each other.
You're what?!
Promised to each other?
Are you kidding me?
That sounds like something
rich people would do.
Wait, you're getting
the wrong idea.
I've known him
since we were little.
Our families are close.
The betrothal's not
formal or anything.
Well, it's formal to me!
Okay, okay.
I see.
That's a lot less gross, then.
I've got enough
money to make sure
you're very well cared for!
[HAYAMA, FUTABA]
Oh, yeah?
I seem to have let the
time get away from me.
I must go now.
But may I see you again?
[YOKO]
Sure.
Yoko is a very special girl,
so I ask you treat her
like the treasure she is.
--[HAYAMA] Got it!
--[FUTABA] Of course!
I'm off then, but
we'll meet again soon!
[YU grunts]
Young Master Takezono.
Haven't seen you in a long time.
You used to work
for the Nishikawas.
Yamaji, right?
What are you doing here?
On my way to bring something
to Miss Yoko, actually.
Jeez, are you still
pretending to be her servant?
How pathetic.
You don't need to
worry about her anymore,
because I'll be taking
care of her.
Psycho stalker.
[YAMAJI]
Ack!
[YU]
Humph.
[YAMAJI]
He's just a child.
A harmless little child.
[HAYAMA] Let's talk about
that kid from yesterday.
Sure, what about him?
He's more than a little
attached to you, eh?
Yeah.
[YOKO] Like I said, our
families are old friends.
It was nice running into him.
[HAYAMA] I'll bet he's
a real sweetheart.
[FUTABA] Rich, too.
Nothing wrong with that, right?
[YAMAJI crying]
Oh yeah, I forgot.
I won't be able to
walk home with you guys
after school today.
Why?
You got something better to do?
It's a family thing.
My cousin's gonna be
staying with us for a week.
So it's my job to pick
her up and escort her home.
I didn't know
you had a cousin.
Oh, how nice!
I'd love to meet her
while she's in town.
Uh, really?
'Cause honestly, I wouldn't
mind having a little backup.
What do you need backup for?
[FUTABA]
Sakura!
Oh! Glad you made it!
[FUTABA] Sorry, were you
waiting a long time?
Yeah! Do you know
how late you are?
Let me introduce you.
These are my good friends,
Yoko and Hayama.
It's very nice to meet you.
Hey, how's it going?
[FUTABA] And this is my
little cousin Sakura.
Hi! It's nice to meet you.
My name is Sakura Usuda.
[YOKO] You are just
the cutest little thing.
I'm aware of that, but thanks!
[FUTABA laughs]
Uh, sorry.
She's got a weird
sense of humor.
Oh, that's all right.
It's nice to meet a young lady
with such self-confidence.
Out of curiosity,
what's with all the luggage?
You don't expect me to travel
without a proper
wardrobe, do you?
I like to be prepared.
What's so weird about that?
This is why you
wanted some backup.
[FUTABA] Maybe we could
use a little more, hm?
You summoned me?
Seriously, dude!
Will you stop doing that?
[SAKURA] I'm not saying I'm
perfect, but I am up there.
I don't see any point
in denying it, do you?
I don't know.
Anyway, I have my
life all planned out.
[SAKURA]
When I turn 14,
I'll be discovered by a talent
scout and become a celebrity.
I'll star in several movies
and TV shows
before getting married
at age 23.
At 25, I'll have a baby boy.
At 28 I'll revive my career
by becoming a model,
and at 50 I'll move overseas
and spend my remaining years
in carefree relaxation.
Pretty sweet plan,
don't you think?
[YOKO] Just remember: you never
know what life might bring.
[HAYAMA, FUTABA]
Aw, how sad.
That guy's kind of handsome.
I wouldn't reject him
because he's a servant.
I'm magnanimous like that.
He's actually not a servant.
Yeah, more like a
stalker who pretends
to have legitimate employment.
Hey!
Oh, really? I'll pass, then.
You're welcome to keep
carrying my bags, though.
[YAMAJI]
You are magnanimous.
[YU]
Hello again!
Yu!
I was hoping I might
run into you today.
Take this. It's wagyu beef
we got as a gift.
Wagyu beef?
[YU]
There's too much for us to eat,
so I wanted you to have some.
Only the best for you.
Yu! [laughs]
[YU grunts]
[YU]
Usuda! What are you doing here?
[FUTABA] Hold on... do you
two know each other?
[SAKURA] Yeah, we're
in the same class.
Right now he's the top candidate
to be my husband someday.
[YU]
Uh, don't I get a say in this?
[SAKURA]
Aw, you're just embarrassed.
[YU]
I am not!
[HAYAMA]
What's the problem?
You'd make a cute couple.
[SAKURA]
You think so too?
[YU]
No! It's never going to happen!
Yoko's the one I'm promised to!
[SAKURA] What do you
mean "promised to"?
You're joking, right?
[FUTABA]
Let's all calm down.
[SAKURA]
Is it over between us?
I thought we had something!
It's something they talked
about when they were kids.
Nothing formal, you know?
I mean, Yoko isn't
even serious about it.
Isn't that right? Yoko?
Wagyu beef for me! Wagyu beef!
No one's home right now.
--[YU] Goodbye.
--[SAKURA] Wait, Yu! Come back!
[HAYAMA]
Think we should stop 'em?
[FUTABA]
Nah, I say let 'em go.
[YOKO]
Beef for me!
So, how did it turn out?
Did the wagyu beef
live up to expectations?
I'm sure it was mind-blowing,
but I wanna hear about
every juicy detail!
Oh, I'm so jealous!
Huh?
I don't think everything
went as planned, okay?
What do you mean?
So much meat.
So much beautiful meat.
Come, now. You can
rise to the challenge.
You can cook this beef, Yoko!
It's so simple. All you need
to do is lightly fry it.
[laughing]
Although the outside
was burnt to a crisp,
the inside was completely raw.
Aw, that sucks.
Cooking meat right
can be tricky.
It can be, but you've still got
a little bit left, don't you?
Not that it does me any good.
Well, if you let me cook
the rest of it, it will.
What?
I told you cooking
is my hobby,
so I gotta show off my skills!
It's high quality meat,
so the important
thing to remember
is not to cook it for too long.
Okay.
[HAYAMA]
Ah.
[FUTABA]
Well, here we go!
Oh, it seems too
good to be true.
I'm not dreaming.
[FUTABA] I still can't believe
you didn't think I could cook.
Don't you have any
faith in me at all?
And considering how
much I like to eat,
I'd be pretty screwed if I
couldn't cook, don't you think?
You kinda come across
as the type of person
who knows how to eat
and not much else.
That's not nice!
You know what,
forget about all that.
We don't want to keep
good beef waiting, do we?
Time to eat, everyone!
[ALL]
Mmm!
[HAYAMA]
This is delicious!
[FUTABA]
It's tender, tasty, and juicy!
[YOKO] Ah! This is what meat
is supposed to taste like.
I gotta say, you have
some pretty impressive skills
in the kitchen.
Aw, I don't usually
make much fancy stuff
since I can't really afford
to eat it on a regular basis.
Actually, my specialty's
a little something
I like to call mama's cooking!
Ah!
Mama!
I humbly accept your worship.
Yes, what is it about
a mother's cooking?
There's something comforting
about it, isn't there?
I remember my mother
used to make
the most wonderful
veal spareribs braised
and then simmered
with chickpeas.
[HAYAMA, FUTABA]
Veal, huh?
It's still one of the best
things I have ever tasted.
In fact, the only
meal I've eaten
that came close
was this one.
Thank you so much.
It's been too long
a time since I've had
a home-cooked meal with
people I truly care about.
We're glad we could be here.
So who's up for seconds?
I say we fry up every last
bit of meat that's left!
Well, if you don't mind.
Of course not, because
eating delicious food
makes people happy
and can soften
even the hardest of hearts!
So from now on,
we need to make sure
you get all the yummy
food you can handle!
Sorry, what are you implying?
You've inspired me!
I'm going to learn
how to cook too.
And I'll invite both of you over
to sample my culinary delights!
I'll be there with bells on!
So what are you
going to make first?
I was envisioning lightly
toasted bread crusts
topped with braised wagyu beef
and freshly-squeezed mayonnaise.
Perhaps you might
consider dusting them
with some pink codfish flakes
and then flambéing them.
I'll take mine on the
crunchy side, with the works!
[ALL laughing]
[FUTABA]
I'll do it!
I'll sell delicious steak for
cheaper than this place!
[FUTABA] And so, the
cooking showdown began.
Futaba went about
to find ingredients.
I think something like
that'll happen next.
[YOKO]
My, that would be good.
A cooking story
needs a taste tester!