[YOKO]
Off to school!
[FUTABA]
Good morning!
[YOKO]
Oh... good morning, Futaba...
...how are... you?
I'm doing great...
Thank you so much for asking!
[FUTABA]
It's gorgeous out.
But on the forecast,
they said there's a good
chance of rain this afternoon...
Can you believe that?
I'm super bummed about it.
Hey, that hurts.
What are you doing?
Ow...
You... are behaving
very strangely...
What's wrong with you?
Uh... what's wrong with me...?
You're the one who's
acting weird, Yoko.
[YOKO]
What are you talking about?
[HAYAMA]
Wait up. Coming.
Man, I am definitely gonna
fall asleep in class...
I almost slept through my alarm,
so it's lucky I'm even
going to school at all.
Heh. Well, I had to skip
breakfast, but we can't be late!
What are you saying?!
All right...
Game's up...
I know what this is.
[BOTH]
What what is?
I've heard of
these pranks before...
It's a hidden
camera type of thing...
You've had your fun...
but that's enough...
As they say "the jig is up."
Honestly, you two...
How long did you think you
would be able to fool me...?
Your acting skills leave a
lot to be desired, you know.
[laughs]
Hayama, I'm scared...
Why's Yoko acting
so strangely...?
Do you think she's sick?
Should we get help?
[YOKO]
I'm not being weird, okay?!
It took two months,
but I finished crocheting
my lace yesterday...
I'm so excited!
Do you want to see it?
Sounds like a
waste of time to me...
If you want lace so bad,
then just buy it.
[FUTABA]
Aw... Don't tease me!
you know this is my hobby...
Look at it. Isn't it the cutest?
Nope, sorry...
that's the lamest hobby ever.
Oh, hi!
Why're you hiding?
Is something wrong?
[YOKO]
So even when I'm not around,
they're still like this...
What is going on with those two?
[BOTH]
Huh?
[NISHIYAMA]
Um... Excuse me.
I... well...
I was wondering...
um... I just...
Jeez, spit it out already.
What's the deal?
Well... you haven't
turned the worksheet in yet...
I've collected everybody
else's already...
...and... since I have to give
them to the teacher all at once,
can I have yours, please?
Whoops...
I guess I forgot
to do it, sorry...
Why don'tcha just take
care of it for me, kay?
Since you're class rep and all.
[NISHIYAMA]
Uh! But... I can't...
[YOKO]
Ah. I get it now...
This is all just a dream.
You should turn it in so
Nishiyama can do her job
and you don't get in trouble
with the teacher... Please!
Jeez...
You look like
you're about to cry...
Fine, I'll take care of it.
[YOKO]
What an awful, awful dream.
[NISHIYAMA]
I hate Hayama so much...!
I hate her, I hate
her, I hate her...
She's a
good-for-nothin' troublemaker
who doesn't care about
anyone but herself,
and one of these days,
she's gonna pay...
I'll teach her to
treat me with respect!
She's different, too.
[KONDO]
That's enough slacking off!
Look how upset
you've made Nishiyama...
Now hurry up and
turn your work in already!
Calm down, will ya?
I'm doing it right now.
You should be nicer to her.
It's not like she's class rep
because she wants to be!
Nobody else felt like
having all the extra work
and responsibility,
so poor, timid Nishiyama
got stuck with the job...
She can't speak up for herself,
so when the teacher asked,
she just agreed.
I guess nothing
will change the way
those two feel about each other.
So tired...!
I could take a nap right here.
You can't do that...!
If you fall asleep now,
you'll miss afternoon classes.
[HAYAMA]
Just five minutes.
[YOKO]
This is too strange...
I don't know how
long I can take it.
They probably
aren't the only ones
who are different...
I wonder what everyone
else is like in this dream.
[laughing]
Whee...! I hate
the world so much!
It's full of nothing
but anger and despair.
Maybe I should
just take this bat
and break all the
windows in the school...
Or I could steal a motorcycle,
except I don't know how to drive
one so I'd probably just die.
Oh, well!
Wow, your sister
is always getting
into all kinds of trouble.
She's got such a bad girl
streak, doesn't she?
Of course.
She totally knows
how to let loose,
unlike some people.
Is that...? Yamaji!
Excuse me, Nishikawa...
Is that how you
address a teacher?
Uh.
I'm so shocked,
I don't know what to say.
What are you doing...?
Have you lost your mind...?
You just punched a teacher!
Oh, whoops... My hand slipped.
I can't believe
you just did that!
And as a matter of fact,
I didn't punch him...
That was clearly a slap.
There is a difference, you know.
That's what we're
gonna focus on?
Inexcusable...!
That kind of violence
is not tolerated here...
Report to the principal's
office immediately.
If somebody has a problem,
they're welcome to come to me.
[YAMAJI] You're only getting
yourself into more trouble.
He's right!
You have to stop! This is crazy!
[SHINO] Now, now...
What's all the fuss about?
[SHINO]
Class will be starting soon...
Return to your rooms at once...
Unless what
you really want--is...
...to experience the
kind of punishment
only Ms. Shino can offer.
[SHINO] That's it.
That's where it ended.
Such a good dream!
[BOTH]
You call that a good dream?!
Where do you come up
with these things...?
Everyone knows
how nice I am to Yamaji.
I would never mistreat
him in such a way.
No... 'course not.
Too bad I woke up right
at the best part...
Maybe if I try really hard,
I can have the same
dream again tonight.
I hafta say...
I'm not a big fan of
the way I came off in it.
It's a dream, nothing personal.
You were weird,
but I wasn't too
different from the real me...
Least I wasn't violent.
I didn't think you were
even in the dream, were you?
Oh, come on!
That was obviously me!
[HAYAMA]
It does sound kinda fun
to be a different version
of yourself, doesn't it?
Especially for you,
since you're usually hiding
your real personality, right?
Eh, heh...
[SAKURA] Oh, there you are...!
Wait up, wait up!
[FUTABA]
Sakura!
[SAKURA]
Well, what do you think...?
Isn't it awesome?
I gave myself a total makeover!
You look adorable.
I know, right?
That's what I was going for,
and I think I totally
nailed it, too...!
So... you know how I'm
gonna be a famous pop idol
when I grow up, right?
Oh yeah...
How could we forget?
I thought maybe you could
listen to one of my songs
if you're not busy right now.
I need to practice
singing in front of people
so I don't get stage fright.
So young and pretty,
like a flower in the spring!
If you want to keep me,
you'd better buy a ring!
Do you know how lucky you
are to have me in your life?
My love will pierce
you like the sharpest knife!
You must know that someday,
I will be your wife!
You will never look at another
girl for as long as you live!
[FUTABA]
Ugh... my poor ears...!
[HAYAMA] Compared
to the way this girl sings,
my sister's actually on key.
[FUTABA]
Please... you gotta stop this!
[HAYAMA] You might want to
practice a little more alone
before performing
in front of people.
[FUTABA]
Yeah...
I heard once that if you're
tone-deaf you can put
a bucket over your
head and it'll help.
[HAYAMA]
Do that!
Oh-kay...
[FUTABA]
She's really doing it...
[SAKURA]
I found a bucket...
So I sing like this?
[FUTABA]
Yeah... I guess.
I've never really
seen it done before.
[SAKURA]
So young and pretty, like--!
So young and pretty, like a--!
[YOKO]
Are you all right?
[SAKURA]
I'm... not so sure about that...
I think I might throw up.
[FUTABA] Good thing
we have a bucket then, huh?
[FUTABA]
I don't know...
[YOKO] I tried to do it
like Sakura had hers.
Hey...! I have an idea.
How about like this? Well?
This would keep it from getting
in my way all the time.
It's missing something,
but I can't put
my finger on what...
Oh I got it...! Glasses, please.
Glasses aren't some
kind of requirement
for wearing braids, you know.
[YOKO] Hmmm... Maybe I should
stop trying different styles
and just cut it shorter.
Why would you do
something like that...?!
Cutting your gorgeous
locks would be a tragedy!
I don't know, I think it might
make for a nice change...
and with all these split-ends,
it would look a
lot healthier, too.
Besides, long hair
requires a lot
of shampoo and conditioner,
and that can get expensive.
No...! You can't do it!
Just think of all the years
of effort that will be wasted
if you cut it...
I mean, you've been
growing your hair out ever
since you were a little girl.
[FUTABA]
Yamaji's right...
You shouldn't do it.
[HAYAMA]
What if you cut it
and then you didn't
like how it looked?
I've always thought your hair
was pretty much perfect,
so, you don't need to
change a thing about it.
You really think it suits me?
Even girls who used
to be rich like you,
can always rock
a princess haircut.
Does what actually looks
good factor in anywhere?
[YOKO] Thanks for coming.
Have a good day!
I've got this down...
Don't you think I've honed
my skills as a cashier...?
I'd consider myself a
professional at this point.
[YAMAJI] You're
absolutely magnificent...!
The best in the world
at anything you do...!
Definitely a professional!
[FUTABA]
Yeah it's very... impressive.
Well... I was shocked when she
got a job in the first place,
so I guess I should
be impressed.
She's like a flower
that grows quickly
when watered with
praise and adoration.
[HIYORI] Look, here it is...!
We found it...
This is the shop
I was telling you about,
the one from the flyer.
[bell chimes]
Welcome! How can I
help you today?
Wow!
What should I get?
They all look so yummy!
[YOKO]
Uh...
What's up? Is something wrong?
Um...
[inaudible]
[SEI]
Nishikawa...? Hi.
Hey, who's that?
[YAMAJI]
A school friend... from before.
It's nice to see you, Osakabe!
Uh! You know her?
Uh. I do, actually...
We were in the same grade
at my previous school.
Ooh... Mannenro
Girls' Academy, right...?
The school where
all the rich girls go.
I didn't know that rich girls
had after-school jobs...
Wait... are you doing it
to learn about the real world?
Actually... my
circumstances changed,
and I'm not what anyone
would call a rich girl now...
I took this job because
I really needed the money.
Ahhhhh...
[YOKO]
We have a large selection,
but these two cakes are our
seasonal recommendations.
[HIYORI] Great.
I'll take one of each, please!
You're right, Yamaji...
I've never seen anything
that was more professional
in my whole life.
Hey, you know...
[SEI] You can give me
a call if you'd like...
Here's my number.
I'd be happy to help
if you ever need it,
so please feel free
to get in touch.
Keep up the hard work,
and I'm sure
everything will be fine.
Thanks for coming.
Have a nice day!
[ALL]
Miss Yoko, are you okay?!
[FUTABA]
Take it easy for now.
You were amazing!
A total professional!
No one could have done better!
Please, it couldn't
have been easier.
Only an amateur would
let something like
that trip them up.
[YOKO] I don't know why
you all seem so surprised.
I told you, I'm a
professional...
[SHINO] Nothing is
more important to you
than your pride,
but you didn't even flinch
when it was threatened!
Now... if you will excuse me,
I believe I will
take a short break...
I'm a bit thirsty,
so I could use a drink.
That's mayonnaise!
[HAYAMA] Heard you had
a rough day yesterday.
It wasn't so awful, really.
It is difficult to have
people from my former life
see my reduced circumstances,
but the fact is, I can't
go back to being who I was.
This is the person I am now,
and I think I can accept that.
Wow, that's mature!
[FUTABA]
Good morning!
Isn't the weather
today beautiful?
So bright and sunshiny!
So what's new?!
Hey, that hurts.
What are you doing?
That's exactly what
you did to her in the dream!
[SAKURA]
You're such a slob!
You need more feminine charm.
Really...?
Why would you say that?
For starters, you're
shoveling food into your face
like a starving monkey!
I spend half the day
with a bucket on my head
because I'm committed
to my dream...!
Maybe you should try putting
effort into something.
Can you believe
she said that to me?
Well...
I never realized
that I was lacking
in the feminine
charm department...
So I decided that
I would prove to everyone
how dainty and girly I can be...
Tee-hee!
You've really
inspired me, Miss Yoko...
I'm going to work
just as hard as you have!
I know you can do it!
Cute...!
Look at the pretty little
birdies having a nice chat.
You're breaking
out in spots all over...!
I think you have hives!
These are really delicious!
Yeah, they sure are.
Hey...!
You want a piece, Odagiri?
Oh, no thank you...
I really appreciate the
generous offer, though...
Tee-hee!
[KONDO]
Uh... are you feeling okay?
Maybe you should go
to the nurse's office.
It's almost lunchtime...
I shouldn't have
sweets right now.
[NISHIYAMA]
You sure you don't want one...?
They're burnt milk caramels.
It's okay. Really, I'll pass.
[KONDO]
You know you're drooling?
[KONDO] So... you don't
think you're girly enough?
If you're looking for pointers,
that's something I should be
able to help you out with...
I maintain a strict beauty
regimen, and it does wonders.
Yeah? What kinda
stuff do you do?
I take rose supplements
and wear perfume to keep
myself smelling nice...
I do stretches to keep
myself limber and flexible...
I do crunches and leg-lifts--
which keeps my figure
trim and well-toned...
I moisturize and exfoliate and
do the occasional chemical peel.
How do you find
time to sleep?
Amazing...! You must spend hours
every day trying to
improve your appearance!
Well, yeah... I want
to better myself...
You got a problem with that?!
[FUTABA]
My lucky number is three...
My lucky color is yellow.
What is that, your horoscope?
That's pretty girly,
isn't it...?
I think I heard before
that girls like looking
at their horoscopes.
[HAYAMA]
We sure do.
[HAJIME]
Hey, where are you going?
I thought you'd be stopping
by Mr. Stuffed's for sure today.
[FUTABA]
Huh?
I can't believe you
haven't heard about
his new yellow
curry challenge!
All you gotta do is eat three
kilos and your meal is free!
Yellow! And three?!
[HAYAMA, YOKO]
Just let it go.
No... I can't.
[HAJIME]
What?!
I don't think I
could ever finish
three kilograms
of food at once...
I'm a dainty little girl.
[HAJIME] What are you doing,
trying to make a fool of me?!
You're Futaba Odagiri!
Don't give up on a challenge
without even trying...!
It's disrespectful to all
those who have lost to you!
Just be yourself...
Go stuff your face.
I second that...
I think the best version
of you is the one
that's smiling the brightest.
[FUTABA gasping]
Okay!
Yum!
Feminine charm level: zero.
[FUTABA]
Thanks for the grub. See ya!
[HAJIME] One of these
days, I'll beat you!
[KOU] Futaba! I heard you were
trying to become more girly...
How's it going so far?
[FUTABA]
Uh... well... you know...
After Teru told me about
it, I made this for you.
[FUTABA]
Stop right there!
I don't want any soup made
from scary, disgusting,
unpronounceable ingredients!
[KOU]
Uh...
It's not soup...
See, it's a drink.
[FUTABA] I think you're
missing the point.
Here.
[HAYAMA]
Drink up... Better you than me.
I brought enough for everybody.
[YU] What happened?
You look different.
You think it worked?
Have our feminine charm
levels really increased?
[YOKO] I didn't think
that we had plans
to meet up today... did we?
[YU] I just had
something to tell you...
My dad said he has
a job for your dad.
Really?! He's going
to hire my father?
That's awesome!
I'm so happy for you.
I'm sure he's gonna want
something in return.
Thank you so, so much...
I don't know how
I can ever repay you.
[YU gasps]
Oh, I dunno...
Maybe you could sign a marriage
application or something.
Well, y'know...
It's not like it would be real
or anything, just for fun...
Like playing pretend.
Hey... that sounds
like a great game.
Let's go play right now!
If anyone needs us,
we'll be submitting
our marriage application.
Ahh! Let me go!
[SAKURA] Did you know I've
been practicing my singing...?
--You wanna hear some?
--[YU] No!
[SAKURA] So young and
pretty, like a flower...!
He's a pushy little guy...
But I don't think he stands
a chance against Sakura.
I am Yoko...
Daughter of the
Nishikawa family.
My father will soon
be gainfully employed
at a respectable company.
[FUTABA]
Whoa!
[HAYAMA]
How fantastically normal!
This is going to change
everything for me!
I won't have to be such
a miser or salivate
over every little scrap of food.
[SASAME]
Um... hi...
I kinda have
something for you...
It's a gift... from me!
For the Valentine's chocolates.
[gasps]
[SASAME] I had a hard time
deciding what to get...
I thought cookies
would be a good idea,
but I wanted the gift
to be useful, too.
You mean... They're mine?
They're all for me?
Yep, that's our Yoko.
It'll take her some
time to adjust.
[HAYAMA] Hold on...
Isn't White Day next week?
What?!
[YOKO sighs]
Still thinking about
them, aren't ya?
I know, I am absolutely
pitiful, aren't I...?
How long have we
been friends now,
and I haven't changed a bit
since the day I met you two.
Are you kidding me?
You've changed a ton!
You really think I have?
Do you remember what
you said when we met?
"I don't recall asking
you to join me...!
Honestly, how rude!"
You sounded just like
a stereotypical rich girl.
A rare and dangerous species...!
So special!
What?
What are you even talking about?
Do you mean endangered species?
Right...
...is that what they call it
when there aren't
very many left of them?
I don't understand why
we're talking about animals
all of a sudden... Sorry.
Hey, do they call
them endangered
'cause they're in
danger of going extinct?
Yup, that's why it's so
important to protect them.
I'm lost...
I honestly don't get what
this has to do with anything.
[BOTH laughing]
[FUTABA] Uh! Another
endangered species!
Huh?!
[HAYAMA]
Good thing...
The world doesn't need
any more of those in it.
any more of what?!
I'm pretty sure they were
talking about you.
Me, why?
That species is already
being protected, though...
...by Kondo.
[YAMAJI]
Why are you wearing that again?!
Come back here!
A strange and fearsome beast.
I don't think we should
get too close to it...
Sonobe!
C'mon! We need to
get out of here.
I hear they'll charge
if you make eye contact.
[HAYAMA]
Another one!
[FUTABA] This one's poisonous...
Beware its venom!
Run away!
[YOKO] Where are you going...?
Wait for me!
[YOKO]
What's gotten into you?
[ALL laughing]
[YOKO]
I thought you should know,
I am graduating
from bread crusts.
[HAYAMA, FUTABA]
Yeah...?!
Today I thought I would try
a bowl of instant
yakisoba noodles.
[HAYAMA, FUTABA]
Wow!
[FUTABA screams]
[FUTABA]
No... I couldn't stop her!
It's all over now. She
put the sauce in first.
You can't eat it like that...!
It's a total noodle fail!
[YOKO]
Huh?
[FUTABA]
Aww, look at her.
[HAYAMA]
She's so cute when she pouts.
[YOKO]
I don't care if they're ruined.
It's not like I enjoy
instant noodles, anyway.
They're such a hassle.
[YOKO] Bread crusts are
inexpensive, abundant,
and delicious.
[FUTABA]
You brought some?
[YOKO]
Mm-hm.
[BOTH laugh]
[laughs]