[SHINO] I cannot help
but feel responsible.
True, my story is
an inspiring one.
She's not really what you'd
call an adventurous dresser.
--More of a plain Jane.
--Huh?!
Welcome to Secret Garden!
Hello! Welcome to Secret Garden!
Teru, hey!
You wanna come
out and play?
Teru, hey! You wanna
come out and play?
Teru, hey! Wanna come out play?
Teru, hey!
Wanna come out and play?
Haven't you ever
heard of a doorbell?
Hey, what's up?
I brought some cards.
You wanna play?
It's like a billion
degrees outside,
and you walked over here
to play a card game?
Yeah, why not?
We'll play Go Fish!
[HAYAMA]
That's the lamest game ever!
If we're gonna hang out,
let's at least
go somewhere cooler!
[FUTABA]
Ah! Blessed air conditioning!
Amen, sister!
[FUTABA] Have you done
the homework we got
for summer break yet?
[HAYAMA]
Yeah, most of it.
I'll take a wild guess
and say that you haven't?
[FUTABA]
Nope.
I figured I could just copy
yours when you were done.
[HAYAMA] Do your own work,
you lazy mooch!
No fair! How 'bout you, Yoko?
[HAYAMA]
Is she sleeping?
[FUTABA]
Sure looks like it.
[HAYAMA]
Um, is your face okay?
Keep your filthy
hands off of me!
How dare you?
[HAYAMA laughs awkwardly]
Don't mind us. Just a little
joke between girlfriends.
[laughs awkwardly]
[FUTABA] So... What's up
with you, sleeping beauty?
I'm really sorry; it's not
that I wasn't having fun.
The cool air is so relaxing, I
guess I dozed off for a second.
You getting sick?
You aren't usually this tired.
I'm okay. I've just
been working a lot.
Still at the cake place, right?
With the weirdly
young-looking maid?
Yeah. I remember now.
You said you were going
to pick up extra shifts
during the break.
I'd probably be there now if
it wasn't closed for the day.
Don't you think maybe you're
working yourself too hard?
Most folks lie down to sleep.
No. I'm fine.
Don't worry about me.
[HAYAMA]
Whoa! That looks so painful!
Not to mention gigantic!
[SHINO]
You fell asleep at the table?
That's both sad and amusing.
I don't think you can work in
the front of the shop today.
Your face might scare
off the customers.
Come on.
It's not really that bad, is it?
It happened 'cause
she's working too much.
[YAMAJI gasps]
This is a travesty!
How could you let
Miss Yoko get injured?!
And on her forehead!
Her lovely face!
Her perfect
aristocratic visage!
What if it leaves a scar?
Have you thought about that?
This is terrible!
You must see a doctor
at once, Miss Yoko!
You're the one who needs help.
But I think he needs a
different kind of doctor.
[YAMAJI]
Ah! The work force is no place
for a delicate flower like her.
You're too soft.
It's time to stop
coddling Miss Yoko.
She's not a child anymore.
[YAMAJI] This is your
fault, devil-woman!
[SHINO]
I'm sorry.
We've known each other for
a long time, but work is work.
I can't give you
special treatment.
I haven't asked
for any, have I?
[SHINO]
I'm glad you understand.
Now, I would appreciate it if
you'd go into the back room
and get some rest.
[YOKO]
Huh?
That's an order.
I prefer my employees
to be well rested.
But I'm all right.
[SHINO] I cannot help
but feel responsible.
True, my story
is an inspiring one.
A humble servant turned
successful business tycoon.
But not everybody has
the strength of character
to travel the path I did.
I blame myself.
In seeking to emulate me,
you came to harm!
Did you hit your head
on something, too?
Hey! Let go!
Your boss said to rest,
so off you go.
No arguing!
What about the shop?
Aren't you going to be
short-handed without her?
You okay?
[SHINO]
What do I do now?
There's no way I can run
this place all by myself!
If it's that big a deal,
why'd you give Yoko the day off?
Hey. I've got an idea.
Why don't you help?
You could take Yoko's
place for a day.
[HAYAMA]
What? Why me?
Come on, it's not like you've
got anything better to do.
[HAYAMA] Says the girl who
wanted to play Go Fish!
Why not volunteer yourself?
We're short on time,
so let's get started.
But those clothes have to go!
Huh?!
[HAYAMA]
Hey! Stop! Get off me!
Nobody said anything
about maid cosplay!
What's wrong?
I thought it would be fun.
Well, it's not! I wanna change.
Why can't I just wear
the same thing Yoko does?
It looks good on you.
That is so not the point!
Are you finished
changing, too?
We should really
be getting to work.
[HAYAMA] This might be worth
the humiliation after all
if I get to see Futaba
in these stupid clothes!
--Ready to go, boss!
--[HAYAMA] Hey!
[SHINO]
My clothes didn't fit her,
so we had to go
with something else.
[HAYAMA]
What didn't fit?
[SHINO] Well, the bust
and hip areas were snug.
I'm not saying she's got
a killer body or anything.
I've always been a bit
on the smaller side.
I'm sure you'll fill
out though, don't worry.
[HAYAMA]
Who said I was worried?
[SHINO]
Oops. I hit a nerve.
It's okay. I'm kind of
a special case.
I haven't grown
since junior high.
Well, to be honest, it was
more like elementary school.
Saying that I have the
body of a 10-year-old
isn't reassuring!
Look on the bright side!
If you stop growing, you won't
have to diet when you get older.
Can we just drop it already?!
Welcome to Secret Garden!
Oh. Where's the usual girl?
Does she have the day off?
Yes ma'am.
We're filling in for her today.
So many young
girls working here.
I bet it makes the
job more fun, huh?
[HAYAMA laughs]
Definitely!
So what can we get you?
Anything in particular
you'd recommend?
Yeah, there's plenty!
Everything's good, really.
I have to say, though, I
especially like this roll cake.
It's simple and light,
made from an airy sponge
wrapped around
luscious buttercream
and infused with the just the
right amount of green tea.
Then of course,
there's the gateau chocolat.
Its refined sweetness pairs
perfectly with a cup
of dark coffee.
The chocolate is sinfully rich,
with just a hint of bitterness.
Finally, the strawberry
mousse cake.
This confection pairs the tangy
sweetness of strawberries
with the lush richness of cream,
creating an explosion of flavor
that will leave you gasping!
You make it so hard to decide!
I guess I'll have
to take all three.
I'll box 'em up right away.
Wow. That was hot.
She makes it sound like
a smutty romance novel.
So... you're up next, then.
Uh, really?
[HAYAMA] It's not like I'm
threatened by Futaba,
but I don't want Sonobe
to think I can't do my job.
Welco--
Welcome to Secret Garden!
Which of our mouthwatering
cakes can I get for you today?
Wow! You really are
dressed up like a maid!
Look at you! You're adorable!
Yeah! I know, right?
Isn't it perfect on her?
You're looking pretty
chic today, yourself!
[FUTABA laughs]
[HAYAMA]
What are you doing here?
I told her you were cosplaying.
You make a great maid, Teru.
Keep up the good work!
Here's some candy
to keep you going!
Oh, what kind of candy is it?
[SHINO] It was very nice
of you to come and visit.
[FUTABA]
She knew just by looking at it!
[HAYAMA] Vampires have
heightened senses, don't they?
[KOU]
Oh, hey!
Maybe I can help bake!
I'll make yummy desserts
with a healthy twist!
I think it'll be perfect!
What d'you say?
Um, maybe.
This is our new gelée.
Its combination of
vitamin C-packed fruit
and collagen make it
great for your skin.
I haven't been able to come up
with a name for it yet, though.
Maybe you can help me
choose something appealing?
[FUTABA]
I'm at a loss.
[HAYAMA] Not sure how
to make it sound appealing.
[KOU]
I know! Gelée de Pork!
[FUTABA]
Gelée de Pork?!
That sounds disgusting, Kou!
Even if it is
scientifically accurate.
Oh!
You mean 'cause collagen
comes from pig skin?
Aw, really? I thought it
had a nice ring to it.
[SHINO] I think I'll
just name it myself.
--[door opens]
--[YU] Yoko!
Yoko! Where are you?
I heard you're working here.
Is it true?
Who's that?
Oh, I recognize him!
[YU]
I know you!
Yes, I was the
Nishikawas' maid.
Young Master Takezono.
Will you people please
keep it down out here?
Miss Yoko will never get her
rest with all this commotion.
Well aren't you
a cute little thing.
You said you're
here to see Yoko?
Yes. I just want to
make sure she's okay.
And, you know, stuff like that.
[SHINO]
That's very sweet of you.
You always were a nice boy.
And adorable, too.
Look at your cute
little bottom.
I see that your birthmarks
have already faded.
Hey! Stay outta my pants, lady!
You freakin' weirdo!
I don't care if you
used to be Yoko's maid!
I can't let her work in
a creepy shop like this!
You're gross and you're
old and I don't like you.
So there!
[KOU]
Sweetie!
Hush! That's not nice.
Good little boys
don't talk like that!
It would hurt your
feelings if somebody said
mean things like that
to you, right? Well?
[YU]
Yes. It would.
[YAMAJI] He's really got a
thing for older women!
Now, I think there's
a sweet little boy here
who just earned himself
a yummy little treat!
[giggles]
Here, candy, just for you!
Thanks. I can't wait to try it!
[FUTABA, HAYAMA groan]
Oh yeah. I almost forgot!
I made this for Yoko.
It'll help her
recover her strength!
[ALL]
Ugh!
[HAYAMA]
Ugh! I think I'm gonna vomit!
My eyes are burning!
Is she licensed
for this kinda thing?
I think we may all
need some hazmat suits!
Hey, Yoko!
I brought some lunch!
[HAYAMA]
No, no, don't do it!
[ALL yelling]
Nishiyama! Wanna hang out?
Nishiyama! Hey!
Nishiyama!
Nishiyama, Nishiyama,
Nishiyama, Nishiyama--
Could you be any
more obnoxious?!
Step away from the doorbell!
[KONDO] C'mon, c'mon!
Let's get something to eat!
[NISHIYAMA]
Where?
Here! It's called Secret Garden.
Their new gelée is
supposed to be amazing!
There were flyers
for it all over school.
[NISHIYAMA]
I can't go.
I'm really trying to
save money right now.
[KONDO]
Huh? For what?
A camera.
[KONDO]
What for?
To take pictures
of my sweet baby.
I don't have the
right equipment.
Wow!
I thought you'd
given up on that by now.
We'll make so many
memories this summer.
I'd like to capture them all.
You know what I mean?
So which of these
looks good to you?
I'm thinking this one.
[NISHIYAMA]
She's not listening.
[CUSTOMERS chattering]
[CUSTOMER 5B]
Great, thank you,
and two of these
gelées, as well.
Sure! Two Gelée de Pork,
coming up!
Futaba, two pigs,
and make it snappy!
Right! Two pigs, got it!
Man, Gelée de Pork
is really popular.
It's going quickly!
Please stop.
That's not its name.
Sonobe, we need
more Gelée de Pork.
We're all sold out!
Gelée de Pork is a hit!
I'm impressed.
Yeah, everybody seems
to like Gelée de Pork!
Of course, 'cause Gelée
de Pork is delicious!
[SHINO growls]
Wow, you seem to
have bounced back
really quickly there, Yoko!
I know! I think it's because
of the food Kou brought me.
[YOKO] I don't know what
her secret ingredient is.
I've felt strangely
energetic since I ate it.
I didn't sleep at all last
night, and look at me!
You look kinda crazy,
to be honest.
[HAYAMA] Well, at least
she's got energy now, right?
Thanks for shopping with us!
Here!
Oh yeah! They're delicious!
[NISHIYAMA whining]
Look! Isn't that Hayama
and her friends?
Welcome to Secret Garden!
How are you girls today?
I hope you didn't come
for the new gelée,
because we just sold out!
[KONDO]
That's exactly what we wanted!
[NISHIYAMA] Well, maybe
we should just leave.
[SHINO] Oh, are these ladies
acquaintances of yours, Hayama?
Yeah, we all go
to the same school!
Yes. Yes, we do.
This is quite a surprise;
I had no idea you worked here.
Do you enjoy it?
Yes, very much.
[SHINO] They're both smiling,
so why does it feel like
they're about to
stab each other?
Whoa! Look at that outfit!
You're dressed like a maid!
Uh... Well, yeah.
So is it like a cosplay thing?
Hey, lemme try!
"Here, master.
I've brought your cake."
This is a uniform,
and therefore not cosplay.
[KONDO] Come on!
It's totally cosplay!
[HAYAMA]
Read my lips, Kondo!
[SHINO]
Stop! Don't poke the bear!
But I saw something
like this on TV before.
Anyway, I don't work here.
I'm just helping out.
Sonobe needed a
couple of extra servers,
so we volunteered.
They're lifesavers, really!
I don't know what we
would do without them.
That's nice of you.
[SHINO] I'm so glad
to have Hayama's help.
She's amazing.
The customers
absolutely adore her.
She works quickly
and efficiently
and can think on her feet.
I don't know if I've
ever met anyone her age
who's that competent.
Aw, you're too kind. Stop.
Please! Working the
counter at a cake shop
is something anyone could do.
I mean, it's not exactly
rocket science, now is it?
I guess it must
be easy to say that
when you've never
done it before.
And I don't know if you could.
You've got so much
pride to swallow,
I'm afraid you might
actually choke on it.
Yes, you're right.
Maybe I'm not cut out for a job
in customer service like you,
since I'm not brave enough
wear an outfit like that.
Yep, it's true!
She's not really what you'd
call an adventurous dresser.
More of a plain Jane.
Don't you ever know
when to shut your mouth?!
And stop acting like an expert!
It's been what, a day?!
[HAYAMA] That sort of
emotional outburst is why
I don't think you
could handle this job.
[SHINO] There's an
easy way to settle this.
Why don't you give it a shot?
Unless you're too chicken.
[NISHIYAMA gasps]
[YAMAJI]
Whoops, I'm sorry about that!
I guess my hand slipped.
It slipped five times?
[YAMAJI] Can't you find another
way to amuse yourself
besides toying with people?
[SHINO]
What?
I don't know what you mean.
My motives were pure.
Is everyone here crazy?!
[NISHIYAMA] No matter what I do,
I can't get away from her.
Let's go back to your
house and stuff our faces!
[HAYAMA] Hold on!
I have something for you.
Really? What?
[HAYAMA]
Go ahead. Take 'em.
Leftovers from a special
order I made myself.
All-natural, organic pet treats!
A gift for your kitty.
Wow, this is good!
[NISHIYAMA]
You're right.
It might be the
best bakery in town.
[KONDO] I can't believe
Hayama works there!
I mean, isn't that crazy?
[KITTEN meows]
You like the treats, huh?
I'm sorry. I don't
have any more for you.
The shop isn't open yet.
[NISHIYAMA gasps]
[SHINO] Does this mean you've
decided to come work for me
after all?
[NISHIYAMA]
What? No!
I was right!
I had a feeling you
might have a change of heart.
Don't worry,
everything's ready for you!
[NISHIYAMA]
Oh, god. What am I wearing?
Remember to smile!
That's the most
important part of the job.
I can't believe this
is my life right now.
Hayama has a great smile.
Really, it just brightens
up the whole room!
I won't ask you to match that,
but you could be
a little friendlier.
I'll show you!
If Hayama can do it,
then so can I!
Hello! Welcome
to Secret Garden!
Well?
Hey! Why are you
taking pictures?
Your "welcome" doesn't
sound very welcoming.
There's something very forced
and unnatural about it.
[NISHIYAMA]
Huh?!
Hmm... Hayama told me
you have a kitty at home.
According to her, you're
extraordinarily fond of it.
I guess so.
Why not imagine
yourself playing with it?
That should help
you look happier.
[NISHIYAMA]
Playing with my kitty?
[NISHIYAMA giggling]
No, never mind.
That would probably
just scare people away.
Wait, let me see!
What did I look like?
[NISHIYAMA]
I'm sorry! Just a minute.
Aw! This sucks!
It's fine, don't worry.
There's no rush.
Thanks! The ribbon's
a little tricky.
Is it your first day here?
You must love wearing
such a cute uniform!
[SHINO] I can see through
that tough exterior
of yours, Nishiyama.
You pretended not to like it,
but that was an act.
You felt special getting dressed
up in your sweet little outfit.
Nice! Keep up the
good work, Nishiyama!
I'm so proud!
[NISHIYAMA] Thanks!
That kinda came outta nowhere.
[NISHIYAMA] I'll take it,
though. Praise is praise.
I shouldn't be surprised.
After all,
anything Hayama can do
should be simple
enough for me.
Yes! I am strong!
I can do anything!
Welcome to Secret Ga--
[FUTABA]
Uh, is that who I think it is?
[NISHIYAMA]
Oh, crap!
I should've seen this coming!
Of course they'd drop by.
They work here!
And now they've
all seen me in this.
Is it too late to duck
behind the counter?
We'll take one dozen
financiers, please.
[NISHIYAMA]
Why's she being nice?
What's going on, Sonobe?
I was wondering why you
suddenly gave me the day off.
Are you replacing
me or something?
Well, Nishiyama has a
massive inferiority complex,
and I thought I might be able
to help her out with that.
[NISHIYAMA]
What? That's not true!
Nice uniform.
Did you just whip
that up last night?
[SHINO]
No.
The truth is I'd
originally designed it
with Miss Yoko in mind.
[YOKO]
Me?
I decided it would be
too tight in the chest area
for her to wear, but it was
the perfect size for Nishiyama.
Ah!
[CUSTOMER 5D]
Excuse me!
Oh! I'll be right there!
[NISHIYAMA]
Man, this place is packed.
I can't keep up.
What'll I do?
[YOKO]
Here, let me help.
It's difficult for anyone
until you get used to it.
So that's a strawberry
mousse, a roll cake,
and a gateau chocolat, right?
[HAYAMA] I'm so sorry.
Thank you for waiting.
We'll take care of
you soon, I promise.
I think you're really
gonna love this one!
It's new and super tasty!
[laughs]
Ooh!
High school girls bonding,
smiling, making nice!
I'm getting younger
by the second!
[NISHIYAMA]
I'm so sorry!
We're all sold out
of Gelée de Pork.
But maybe you'd like to try this
green tea roll cake instead?
Great! You'll love it!
[sighs] Man, I'm not used
to working that hard.
[NISHIYAMA]
Oh, well. It was worth it.
I got these kitty treats.
And now...
[SHINO]
Hello.
It's a small world, huh?
What are you doing here?
[NISHIYAMA] I'm just looking
around for a good camera
so I can take better--[gasps]
That's me!
Why are you printing those out?
[SHINO] I thought they'd
make nice mementos.
I don't need them!
You mean you don't
need mementos
because you're going
to keep working for me?
What?! Never mind!
Just delete those
from your phone!
I mean it! Right now!
[SHINO]
This is Shino...
[NISHIYAMA] ...and Selina's
next episode preview!
[SHINO] Nishiyama,
you're a capable woman,
so I leave this to you.
Thank you.
[NISHIYAMA]
What? Well, fine.
Next time:
"Veggies, Meat, Meat, Meat,
Meat, Meat, Meat and Fish."
Please watch!
You made me do it,
so what's with that reaction?