[YOKO] It's not because nobody
else was willing to eat with me,
all right?
[FUTABA]
We didn't think it was.
Wait, hold on. Do you not
have any friends at all?
[YOKO]
Are you always this direct?
The poor thing was
crying pretty hard
by the time it was over, though.
I wonder if it was
something I said.
[STUDENT 1A]
I'm starving!
Can we eat already?
[STUDENT 1B]
Sorry I'm late!
[STUDENT 1E]
I swear, it's true!
[STUDENTS laughing]
[STUDENT 1H]
Did he really say that?
[STUDENT 1I]
Yep, word for word!
[STUDENT 1H]
Wow, that's hilarious!
What'd you tell him?
[HAYAMA]
Oh, no, I don't mind at all.
I just want to do the best
I can as class representative.
[STUDENTS chattering]
[STUDENT 1M]
Slow down. Wait for me!
[STUDENT 1L]
C'mon, just hurry up!
[HAYAMA]
Huh?
[CAT meows]
[HAYAMA squeals]
[FUTABA] Move, people!
Out of the way!
Whoops, sorry! Coming through!
Ugh! I'm so hungry!
If I don't eat soon,
I'm gonna pass out.
And then I'll miss
my next class!
[laughs] I'll just
have to get creative.
There has gotta be a shortcut
around here I can take.
[HAYAMA laughing]
[FUTABA, HAYAMA gasp]
Excuse you!
Hey, hey, hey!
What are those you're eating?
Well, what do they look like?
These are bread crusts,
thank you!
[HAYAMA]
Wow, pig out much?
That's a lot of food!
[FUTABA]
It's not that much!
I'm actually being kind
of restrained today.
Oh yeah?
[FUTABA] Personally, I wonder
how you can eat so little.
Is that really enough to keep
you going all day long?
[HAYAMA] My body is just
more efficient than yours.
I don't need all this.
Do you want some?
Yeah, I do! Woo-hoo!
You can have some too,
if you want.
What's the matter with you?
Don't you have any manners?
I don't recall asking either
of you to join me for lunch.
Honestly, how rude!
Ah! That was amazing!
Oh, come on,
say it again!
Please? You sound like
a perfect little rich girl!
[FUTABA laughing]
Easy, now.
Practice restraint, remember?
[YOKO]
Are you joking?
I don't even know how
to respond to that!
Guess we are being rude.
We haven't even introduced
ourselves yet, have we?
My name is Hayama.
I'm doing Class 3 the favor
of being their representative.
Is that so? Lucky them.
And this is Futaba Odagiri,
Class 3's glutton.
How's it goin'?
Well it's a pleasure
to meet you.
My name is Yoko Nishikawa,
and I'm in Class 2.
Yeah, we know.
Everyone here does.
You're famous.
[YOKO gasps]
Famous?
So... I may have told someone to
keep their filthy hands off me,
but last I checked
it wasn't a crime
to value one's personal space!
Actually, that's the first time
I've heard this story.
And however it looks,
I'm eating alone
because I want to.
It's not because nobody else
was willing to eat with me,
all right?
Okay. We didn't think it was.
Wait, hold on.
Do you not have
any friends at all?
[YOKO]
Are you always this direct?
I don't have much in common
with the other students.
We're just too different.
How can I talk to anybody if I
don't know what to talk about?
[laughs] It can't be that hard.
We're talking
just fine right now.
[FUTABA]
Uh-huh.
That breeze...
This is really great.
I'd forgotten how lovely
it can be to eat outside.
Well, maybe--
--[bell rings]
--Oh, there goes the bell.
Oh no!
[FUTABA]
Okay, all done!
See you around, Yoko!
[HAYAMA]
Catch you later!
Oh. Yeah. All right.
Hey, just so you know,
bread crusts are really yummy
when you deep fry 'em and
sprinkle some sugar on top.
You just fry them in oil?
And add sugar?
I never thought of that.
Could you write
down the recipe--
[FUTABA]
Sorry, we gotta get going!
[HAYAMA] Our teacher gets super
angry whenever people are late!
--English is next.
--[STUDENT 1T] Yup.
How was the homework?
Did you get it done?
[YOKO]
Those girls were so strange.
I'm not sure what
to make of them.
But still...
They were nice enough
in their own way, I suppose.
And that was the first time
I haven't eaten lunch alone
since I came to this school.
[YOKO]
Class 3. So this is theirs.
I could barely
keep my eyes open.
Yeah, I hear you.
[STUDENT 1W]
Is that Nishikawa?
[STUDENT 1V]
What's wrong with her?
[YOKO sighs] I'm so glad I
made it before the sale ended.
Look at all this food!
Hey. Just so you know,
bread crusts are really yummy
when you deep fry them
and sprinkle some sugar on top.
[YOKO]
Let's see...
I'll need oil, and
hopefully I have some sugar.
[bell ringing]
[FUTABA]
Finally, lunchtime!
I thought I was gonna starve!
Watch yourself!
I think being class rep
is going to your head.
Sorry, Nishiyama.
I don't know what you mean.
Yes, you do.
Or did you forget about
how you badmouthed Kondo
to the teacher yesterday?
There must be
a misunderstanding.
All I did was deliver
the printouts he wanted.
I'm not exactly sure why
Kondo didn't do it,
since she was the one on duty.
[laughs nervously]
Well... that doesn't matter.
I still think we should settle
this with a little private chat.
Follow me.
[HAYAMA]
Sure, if that's what you want.
Try not to be
too hard on her.
Whatever. I don't take
orders from you, okay?
[FUTABA] Um... I was
actually talking to Hayama,
but never mind.
[HAYAMA laughs]
[YOKO]
It was a bit of a challenge,
but I hope they like it!
[YOKO shrieks]
I'm here! And I
brought a surprise.
Well, it's not like we
actually agreed to meet again.
And now I can go back
to enjoying a solitary meal,
just like before.
I like it this way. Really.
[rustling]
[FUTABA]
That was a stupid way to go.
I'm all scratched up!
What a surprise. It's you.
You're the one who
insisted we take a shortcut.
Well I didn't want to keep
Yoko waiting for too long.
I thought you'd
forgotten about me.
[FUTABA]
Did you have to wait long?
[HAYAMA]
I'm so sorry.
Yes. It's been five minutes!
I hope you have a valid excuse!
I do, actually.
Someone decided they
wanted to pick a fight with me.
What? Oh no!
Are you all right?
Yep!
The poor thing was
crying pretty hard
by the time it was over though.
I wonder if it
was something I said.
[FUTABA]
Trust me on this.
It's best not to ask.
[rustling]
Huh? Who's in there?
I bet it's some freaky stalker.
They go around hiding
in bushes, right?
[YAMAJI yells]
[ALL scream]
Yamaji!
[HAYAMA]
You know this guy?
[YOKO]
I do. He's my former servant.
[YAMAJI] Please,
forgive me for intruding!
Okay...
Calm down. Explain yourself.
[YAMAJI] I'm sorry, but I had to
know for sure what I'd seen.
Was yesterday's encounter
fleeting or would it endure?
So you were in the
bushes yesterday too?
Yes, and I admit I was
shocked by what I saw.
I was convinced that
it would take a miracle
for Miss Yoko to make friends.
Hey, what's that
supposed to mean?
[YAMAJI] With your family
company's bankruptcy,
you're a shadow of the rich
young lady you once were!
Even so, your upbringing
makes it difficult
for you to forsake the
upper-class attitudes
you've embraced all your life.
So for you to befriend
the everyday folk
who attend your new school...
It must surely be a miracle!
Wow...
It's not like that at all.
Yamaji, you're
obviously exaggerating!
[YAMAJI]
I beg you!
Look after Miss Yoko as
she starts her new life!
Be her true friends!
Boy, that was fascinating!
Should we eat?
But I...
You know I'm down.
Listen, I can explain.
What Yamaji said
may be partially true.
[HAYAMA]
It's so nice out today.
Eating on the grass...
Surrounded by nature.
Are you ignoring me?
Oh. I was right!
I knew you would never really
be able to make friends!
--That's enough, Yamaji!
--I'm sorry. But... It's true.
[HAYAMA laughs]
[STUDENTS chattering]
[YOKO]
Honestly!
Must they insist on
making all this noise?
I mean, we are here
to learn, aren't we?
But it's impossible with
all this constant chatter.
I couldn't imagine
trying to make friends
with girls like these.
So loud and unladylike.
[FUTABA]
Hey, over here, Yoko!
What's up?
Oh, hi!
What are you doing here?
Ugh! Think we could
take it down a notch?
[YOKO] What did you
want to talk to me about?
I need a favor.
I sorta left my
math book at home.
Maybe you could
let me borrow yours?
I do wish I could help,
but my class doesn't
have math today,
so I didn't bring it.
Aw, you didn't?
Really? That's too bad!
I'm sorry! Forgive me!
I promise, if my means
weren't so badly diminished,
I would have a servant
fetch it for you.
Oh, no, it's really
not that big a deal.
Anyway, see you later.
[FUTABA]
Let's eat! I'm wasting away.
I apologize for not being
able to help you earlier.
Are you talking
about the textbook?
No, no! It's my bad for
not bringing it with me.
Not having her book
isn't going to make
that big of a difference
to Little Miss ADD
over here anyway.
Exactly! Huh?
[FUTABA] Do you realize
when you're being mean,
or do you just talk
before you think?
[HAYAMA] I was just
telling the truth.
Forget it. I don't even care.
Right now I just wanna eat!
Uh... what in the
world are you eating?
You really don't know?
This is called bread.
I know what bread is.
What I don't get is why
you're eating a whole loaf.
Well, it's filling, and it's
easier than making a sandwich.
Do you realize when
you sound like an idiot?
What about you?
Are you having bread
crusts again today?
Yeah! You can get
so many of them
for such little money!
When I first saw
these in the store,
I thought it was
too good to be true.
[FUTABA] That doesn't really
make for a balanced lunch,
though.
Fortunately, I discovered
something to solve that problem.
There, you see?
It's perfectly nutritious!
[FUTABA]
Um, not exactly.
[sobbing]
[YAMAJI crying]
My poor Miss Yoko!
You've fallen so far!
Gaaah!
Yamaji?
You know if you keep trespassing
on school grounds like this
I'll have to call the police.
Oh, I'm not trespassing.
I'm in charge of refilling
the vending machines.
It's a side job.
[HAYAMA] Never mind, then.
It's all good.
This guy's a stalker!
How is it "all good?"
That is absolutely unfair!
The only thing I'm doing
is watching quietly
from the shadows
without anybody knowing,
and you're calling
me a stalker?
[FUTABA]
That's basically the definition!
It's completely innocent.
I'm only concerned about
Miss Yoko's welfare.
My grandfather had this job.
When he passed away,
I took over for him,
and then the company
went bankrupt.
So taking care of her
is my family's legacy.
I can't help but worry how
she'll make the adjustment
to being among the common folk.
She has such an
explosive temper, you see.
If everything doesn't go exactly
the way she wants them to,
terrible things--
That's enough!
[YAMAJI]
Here, I want you to have these.
They're clearance goods
from the vending machines.
Expired, but only barely!
But... I don't need this.
Whoops.
I think I'm gonna be
late for my next job.
I'll see you later.
[FUTABA] It seems like
it would be way easier
to just give you cash,
don'tcha think?
Something tells me
that he doesn't have
a lot of money to spare.
Truly, I don't know
what's the matter with him.
Does he really think
I want all this stuff?
Well, he couldn't be
more wrong about that!
Hey, you're kinda glowing.
[YOKO] Every time I start
to feel more at ease,
Yamaji shows up
and humiliates me.
I've finally made
some friends here.
I don't want anything
to scare them away!
[YAMAJI]
Here you go.
Today's expired
vending machine goods.
They're all yours.
[YOKO] Couldn't he at least find
a more private time to do this?
Fine! If you insist,
I'll take them
Excellent. I'm off then. Bye!
[YOKO]
Stay calm, Yoko, stay calm.
No matter what you see,
don't squeal with delight.
They'll think you
have no self-control.
[YOKO squeals]
Do you see that? It's cheese!
Wow, that's exciting.
I'm happy for you.
Yeah, cheese is healthier
than a lot of that other stuff.
[HAYAMA]
I've got a question.
If you had to eat one food every
day, what would you choose?
White rice.
I'd assumed you
would say bread.
I guess I kinda consider
bread more like a snack.
Rice is good 'cause it goes
with just about anything.
Then why don't you pack
something with rice?
I don't have enough time
for that in the morning.
Okay, What's your favorite?
Me? Oh, that's easy!
I... love... mille-feuille!
[HAYAMA] Ugh! Fine!
It's salty fish paste.
You got a problem with that?
No. No problem at all.
Oh! Yeah, that
stuff is delicious.
It goes really well with rice!
What about you, Yoko?
I bet it's cheese.
[YOKO]
I need to be careful.
I have to choose an answer
they won't think is strange.
Something pedestrian.
Something regular people like.
Flan's delicious,
don't you think?
Ew, no way!
But flan would be
totally gross with rice!
Does that matter?
[YOKO] Is that what
normal people like?
Foods that pair well with rice?
I need to try a
different answer.
Uh... pink codfish
flakes sure are tasty.
[FUTABA]
Codfish flakes?
I know! Mayonnaise!
Well, at least that
sounds more like the truth.
Don't take this the wrong way,
but are you sure
you used to be rich?
Well, I uh...
[YOKO]
It's hopeless.
I can't seem to say
the right thing.
What if they start to hate me?
I'll have to eat alone again.
[rice cooker beeping]
[YOKO] I shouldn't worry.
It'll be fine.
[YOKO] After all,
They were impressed with
the fried bread crusts.
I'm sure they'll like these too.
Come on, ladies!
Aren't you ready for lunch?
I have a surprise for you!
Presenting my very
first batch of rice balls.
[BOTH]
Whoa!
[FUTABA] I thought she lived
on a diet of bread crusts.
Who knew all this time
I've had hidden culinary skills?
I can't make 'em.
I'm impressed you were
able to learn so quickly.
It was simple,
and there're plenty here,
so feel free to dig in!
Do you think she means
balls of just rice?
No. No way.
Those look like plain
balls of rice to me.
You mentioned yesterday
how much you loved it,
so I thought these
would be perfect.
That's true.
Rice is my favorite.
What I like most about it
is how versatile it is.
Like how rice balls can have
so many different fillings.
I didn't realize they were
supposed to have filling.
Really?
I thought about adding
salted fish paste,
since Hayama likes it so much,
but it was expensive.
You were gonna do that
just for me?
That would have been an
interesting choice, all right.
The trickiest part
about making them
is getting the
perfect salt level.
[YOKO gasps]
The salt!
I was afraid I'd
forgotten something!
[YOKO]
Oh no. I did it again.
I made a fool of myself.
I thought I was making
something really special.
Stupid Yoko.
[FUTABA]
Are we gonna eat or not?
Thanks for cooking.
That was sweet of you.
[FUTABA]
Mind if I have another one?
You don't have to.
Please don't eat them
just to make me feel better.
Hey, I told you
rice is my favorite!
Well, in that case...
Have as much as you want!
[stomach growls]
[laughing]
[FUTABA]
Come on, Yoko!
It sounds like you
need to eat, too.
[HAYAMA] Would you like one
of my Vienna sausages?
[YOKO] Thank you,
that sounds wonderful!
[FUTABA] Just one more,
then I'll stop!
[HAYAMA snorts, laughs]
[YOKO] You don't have to
do anything to thank me
for cooking.
I was happy to do it.
I wanted to.
Because we're friends.
Don't be so shy.
Not around us.
Loosen up, since we're
friends and all!
If it makes you feel better,
they were free tickets.
I kinda have something of a hook
up for random stuff like this.
Here we are!
[YOKO]
A bathhouse!
[ALL]
Ahh!
Nothing like a nice
hot bath to ease the mind
and relax the body.
I hear ya.
And it smells wonderful.
This is absolutely amazing!
I can barely remember
the last time I had a bath
that was this luxurious!
Wait!
It must take a lot of
energy to heat enough water
for a bath this big.
I can't even imagine how high
the utility bills must be!
Relax already!
[YOKO]
I lost it a little. Sorry.
[HAYAMA, FUTABA laugh]
[YAMAJI]
A little spa time!
If that's not girl bonding,
than I don't know what is!
I was worried, but
it looks like Miss Yoko
will be okay.
I think it might be
time for you to get out.
[YOKO] But it was so kind
of Hayama to bring me here.
I don't want to waste it.
Don't worry about it!
It was free, remember?
I should stay an hour longer.
No. Maybe a whole day longer.
If you're not careful,
you'll pass out!
Yeah!
You're gonna turn into
Yoko soup pretty soon!
Ahh... No, really I'm good.
[FUTABA, HAYAMA]
Yoko!
[YOKO] And so my
tumultuous school life began.
This new dog eat dog
world is full of trials,
such as understanding
how to spend break time!
But from now on...
I won't lunch alone!
[FUTABA] Shall we eat
indoors when it rains?
[YOKO]
Yes.