[SHINO] The answer
is school uniforms.
You can leave the curry
to me, Fearless Leader!
We're gonna go visit Hanako!
Look, people are
even running for it!
I won't be a ghost, though.
I shall be playing
the part of a zombie.
I will see what
advice she can offer.
I think we should
do a restaurant.
Yeah, and we can cosplay!
We could make a
haunted house.
How about fortune telling?
I like that!
Ugh, how boring.
So what do you
think we should do?
I bet you've got
some amazing ideas.
Don't hold back.
What are they?
Well, a cat café.
[CAT meows]
Maybe.
A cat café?
Or we could do dogs instead.
I think cats would probably
be more popular, though.
Right, everyone.
Let's hear what you've
all come up with.
And be sure to
explain your entire plan
including decorations
and materials,
an ordering system
if you're serving food,
costume production, work shifts,
and tear-down process.
Who would like to share first?
Come on, don't be shy.
So, a presentation
on the merits
of different cell phones.
Do we have any other ideas?
How the heck are we
supposed to come up
with all those details?
[STUDENT 9B]
Right?
[STUDENT 9C]
Yeah.
[STUDENT 9D]
This is too hard!
[FUTABA]
I know! Pick me! Over here!
[HAYAMA]
Okay, Odagiri! What do you got?
A curry shop!
Since the cultural festival
only happens once a year,
I think we should do
something really cool!
[HAYAMA]
All right. A curry shop.
Are we going to have costumes?
We should pick something
that'll be easy to make.
[SHINO]
The answer is school uniforms.
Think about it: curry
made by high school girls
wearing uniforms
and cute aprons.
No one will be able
to resist that.
Costumes wouldn't be effective
if they were cheap-looking
and hastily thrown together.
So we'll just work
with what we have.
Uniforms are the way to go.
What do you say,
ladies of Class 3?
Are you with me?
[SHINO chuckles]
Hey! She's from the cake shop!
Huh? No, that's impossible!
It's not her. She can't be here!
Good idea!
Totally! Why bother making
costumes if we don't have to?
So all we need are aprons.
I've already got one of those!
Hold on a sec.
Is that girl even in our class?
[STUDENT 9C]
Where did she go?
She's so tiny that
all she has to do
is put on a school uniform,
and she blends right in.
[NISHIYAMA]
She shows up everywhere!
Is no place safe?
[FUTABA] So that's how we
decided to wear our uniforms
instead of making costumes.
Sonobe...
I think a curry
shop's a good idea,
since so many people like it
and it's easy enough to make.
[FUTABA]
And it smells so yummy!
Do you have to do
a lot of extra work
since you're the
class representative?
Not as much as you'd think.
I have Nishiyama
to thank for that.
All I had to do was
stroke her ego a bit,
and she was eager to help out.
[YOKO]
Wow!
[FUTABA] It's sad how
easy she is to flatter.
She likes feeling important,
so give her that,
and she'll do anything.
So what's your class
gonna do for the festival?
We decided to put
together a haunted house.
Doesn't that sound like fun?
Not to me it doesn't.
I've never done
one before, though.
I was hoping you
could tell me about them.
Don't look at me!
I don't do haunted houses!
Are you all right?
Aw, what's wrong?
Is poor wittle Futaba
scared of ghosties?
Yeah! Ghosts are totally creepy.
You can't see
them or touch them,
so you can't punch them
if they attack you.
I won't be a ghost, though.
I shall be playing
the part of a zombie.
A zombie?
That's better, right?
You can punch those.
But they're gross!
[NISHIYAMA] I decided it
makes the most sense
to use our desks as tables,
but we don't want them
to get covered in curry,
so we need to use
something to protect them.
Tablecloths are hard to clean,
so I went with paper
placemats instead.
You always come up with
the most brilliant ideas.
Whenever we have one of
these big school events,
I'm always glad I don't
have to be in charge.
I think that everyone's glad
you don't have to be in charge.
Where would we be
without Nishiyama,
our fearless leader?
Are you making fun of me?
I wanna help, too.
You can leave the curry
to me, Fearless Leader!
[FUTABA] Today's extra-large
challenge is curry?
[SHOP OWNER] All right.
Let's see what you can do!
[chuckling]
[FUTABA]
I'mma crush this bowl, for one!
Just watch me!
[SHOP OWNER]
Ready, go!
Okay, that's it. Time's up!
[FUTABA]
I couldn't finish.
There's no way anyone
could finish that!
It's too spicy!
Somebody won the
challenge yesterday,
so I was starting to think
it must be too easy.
I figured you could
do it for sure.
What?!
I guess if you don't have a
soul, you also can't feel pain.
[HAJIME laughs]
The curry's too spicy for you?
Wow, what a baby!
What?
I never have trouble eating
spicy food; know why?
'Cause I'm not a
pathetic baby like you!
Let me show you how it's done!
[HAJIME]
Aww!
Poor thing.
My mouth's on fire!
That's strange.
Well, I dunno what went wrong.
Guess I'll have to go back to
the drawing board on that one.
It's not free since
you didn't finish,
but you're both regulars,
so I'll just charge
you 50% for the curry.
Really? Thank you!
I'd hate to waste this,
so I'll take it to-go.
Yeah! Me, too!
[FUTABA]
What a week!
Yesterday I did a whole
bunch of curry research.
Did you steal that pot
from the Stuffed Hut?
[FUTABA]
It's really spicy,
but if I add more
veggies and stuff,
that might tone it down.
[HAYAMA] I'm not eating
your old curry.
Everybody knows curry tastes
better on the second day!
The cultural festival is
still days away, though.
Well, I can at least use Mr.
Stuffed's curry as a reference.
That way I'll know
what spices to put in it.
No need to get carried away.
We don't have the budget for
a bunch of gourmet spices,
and it'll just be easier if
we go with a store-bought roux.
It's a school festival,
so people won't
expect much, right?
That's the spirit!
Mediocre curry
will be good enough!
Everyone will buy and
prepare the ingredients
they're in charge of.
We'll be serving
in disposable dishes.
So it should be--
I'm still a little
nervous, though.
I've made curry a ton of times,
but never in such a
large amount at once.
Any curry questions
go to Odagiri.
That's her area.
[STUDENT 9D]
Hayama!
What do you think about
the decorations so far?
[HAYAMA] Ask Nishiyama.
She's in charge of décor.
Nishiyama!
[HAYAMA] Getting ready for the
cultural festival
is usually really difficult,
but with those two
being so unexpectedly helpful,
things are going smoothly.
[YOKO]
Um...
[HAYAMA] Okay, so you're
worried about the haunted house
because you don't know how
to do your zombie makeup?
That's right.
Everybody else seems
to know exactly what to do
for their scary costumes,
but I'm totally at a loss.
Why don't you ask
Tsuji to help you?
I thought about that, but...
[STUDENT 9G] Aw, cute!
But what if we try this?
She seems to be very
popular with our classmates.
I can see why.
She reminds me
of a small animal.
What are you ladies
chatting about over here?
You look so serious.
I have a problem.
[KONDO] All right.
Let's go to the bathroom.
[FUTABA]
Why would we do that?
We're gonna go visit Hanako!
[FUTABA] You say that like
you're going to drop in
on an old friend or something!
You have fun, but I'm not going!
I'm sure she's very busy and
won't have any time to see us!
But...
Nishikawa needs help, and
she's your friend, isn't she?
Yeah, of course she is!
I'll help some other way.
I don't like scary things!
Because you can't eat them?
Why can't people understand
that not everything's
about food to me?!
I'm not familiar with Hanako.
Who is she?
[FUTABA gasps]
Oh, wow.
I can't believe you've
never heard of her.
She haunts the bathrooms here--
Not listening!
I'm not listening!
♪ La la la la... ♪
[FUTABA]
Are they done? Is it safe?
[FUTABA] She's actually
interested in this stuff?
What a great idea!
Let's see if we can meet Hanako
and somehow convince
her to help us out!
[FUTABA] I can't let you
do this! It's too dangerous!
What if she gets angry and drags
you into a toilet or something?
I will see what
advice she can offer.
[KONDO]
Well, you ready?
Yes, let's go.
[FUTABA]
No! Come back!
If anyone needs me, I'll be
preparing for the festival.
Hey, wait!
Well, I'm all alone now.
[FUTABA]
I'm scared. What should I do?
Maybe I should head
back to the classroom too.
Odagiri.
[FUTABA screams]
It's the ghost of the
moody and obnoxious
high school girl
who haunts these halls
because she could never be
anything more than second best!
Get up!
[FUTABA] Oh my god!
It's speaking to me!
You're supposed to be
in charge of the curry,
so come in here and do your job!
Kondo seems to be AWOL, too.
Honestly, you're all
a bunch of slackers!
You might never
see Kondo again.
She and Yoko are trying
to track down Hanako.
Really? The ghost
from the bathrooms?
I don't understand those idiots.
What's the point in doing that?
To seek advice, apparently.
They must be up to something!
What is it?
Well, scaredy-cat,
we made it back alive!
So did you find her?
We thought about it,
and who wants to spend time
searching every
toilet in school?
It sounded like
way too much work.
Yeah, not to mention
super grody!
[laughing]
[YAMAJI]
A zombie?
Miss Yoko... You're kidding!
[YOKO] I know that I'm
supposed to dress up
and scare the
haunted house visitors,
but I don't know exactly how
I'm supposed to look or act.
So of course I thought
of you, Sonobe.
You're inhumanly
stealthy and emotionless.
Maybe you can give me some
tips on how to be a monster?
I don't understand
what you mean.
I move and feel as any
other human being does.
[YAMAJI]
This is wrong!
It's obvious that you're
not the zombie type.
They're the lowliest monster.
You should be playing
a noble creature.
Do your classmates not
understand you at all?
I would expect your teacher
to know better, at least!
We will do what we
can to help, Miss Yoko.
You shall be the
best zombie ever.
I am so looking
forward to the festival!
I will be there to see your
haunted house, of course.
And so will I!
To support me?
That is nothing more than
I would expect from you.
Yes.
[SHINO]
Brown noser.
[YOKO]
Oh, and, Sonobe...
I hear that you sneaked into
Class 3 and posed as a student.
Have we not
talked about this?!
[ANNOUNCER] Hello, and welcome
to Central High School's
32nd cultural festival!
I hope you're excited!
[applause]
[ANNOUNCER] Our theme this year
is "Beautiful Metamorphosis."
We hope everyone will enjoy
our students' hard work
and help to make this
festival the best one yet!
[NISHIYAMA]
All right.
The curry definitely
smells ready to me!
Okay, everybody, are
we ready to get started?
[STUDENTS]
Yeah!
Eating probably isn't the first
thing people will wanna do.
[FUTABA]
Two bowls, please!
What?
[FUTABA]
Hmm... Uh...
Let's make it three!
Already?
I won't have any
energy unless I eat,
and it'll be good advertising.
Come on in!
[STUDENT 9H]
We'll read your fortune!
What should we do?
[FUTABA]
Mmm!
Wow! This is delicious!
[FUTABA] This curry's flavor is
so simple and comforting.
It tastes like it was made by
high school girls in aprons.
Yummy!
[STUDENT 9J]
Welcome!
We're serving curry made by
high school girls in aprons!
[FUTABA]
So this curry really is made by
high school girls in aprons?
Wow! I'll take
another bowl, please!
[NISHIYAMA]
Thanks! Enjoy the festival!
Check it out!
There are so many people here!
Yeah, but I bet I
can bring in more!
We could send Futaba
out to advertise.
Leave it to me!
Ugh. Anything to get
her away from the food.
[HAYAMA]
I always forget how many people
come to this thing every year.
[FUTABA]
Me too.
All right, let's get us
some customers!
Curry!
Isn't one of the classes
selling curry today?
Let's go check it out.
Delicious homemade curry,
prepared by Class 3.
Right this way!
Awesomely mediocre!
Wow, huh?
I can't believe how
well this is working!
Look, people are
even running for it!
[CROWD yelling]
[FUTABA, HAYAMA]
Huh?!
[BOTH scream]
--[MAN 9A] Run away!
--[GIRL 9B] Ow!
[FUTABA]
What's going on?
[gasping, groaning]
[FUTABA]
Huh?
You hear that?
Something's coming!
[gasping, groaning]
[BOTH scream]
[YOKO growling]
[HAYAMA]
What's up with that eye?
[band playing]
[HAYAMA]
Advertising.
You were doing the
same thing we were.
[FUTABA]
I don't know how much longer
I can keep from freaking out!
[HAYAMA] You put a lot into this
just for a cultural festival.
Do you like it?
Sonobe helped with the makeup.
Surprisingly, doing makeup
is a lot like icing a cake.
I don't even wanna
know what kind of cakes
you've been making lately.
I swear you weren't
there a second ago.
It's strange.
Almost everybody runs the
other way whenever I approach
to tell them about
the haunted house.
Commoners don't know what
to do when someone of your rank
speaks to them, and so they
shrink back out of fear and flee
because they feel unworthy.
[YOKO]
Oh, hello, Yamaji.
[HAYAMA] Now his sudden
appearances I'm used to.
Miss Yoko, the thing
they fear is your eminence.
You think that's what it is?
I'll take a wild guess and
say it's the zombie makeup.
Also, your acting is so
realistic that it makes them
tremble with terror!
[HAYAMA]
Nope, sorry.
I think I'm gonna
stick with my answer.
[HAYAMA] So, is the
haunted house going well?
[YOKO]
It's been fairly busy.
I've spent most of my
time advertising, though.
Sorry, but there's
no way I'm doing it.
It's made by a
bunch of teenagers.
How scary could it be?
[FUTABA gasps]
[FUTABA]
Yeah, that poster's pretty lame.
Maybe I can do this.
Come on. Let's go in.
[FUTABA whimpers]
[SASAME] I hoped you would
come, Futaba Odagiri.
Now I've got the chance
to humiliate you
the way you've
humiliated my brother!
Y'know, it's darker
than I expected.
Yeah, I can't see anything.
[FUTABA whimpering]
Soon!
Boo! Feel my vengeance!
[FUTABA] I wish there was a
little more light in here.
[SASAME]
Here's a flashlight if you want.
Right here. Go on, take it.
[FUTABA]
What? Where?
[ALL scream]
[WOMAN 9C] Whoa,
did you hear that scream?
[WOMAN 9D] Yeah, it must
be a killer haunted house.
[STUDENT 9K] Please,
just make a line over here.
Everyone will get
a turn, don't worry!
Looks like I attracted customers
to the haunted house, too.
You sure are
good for business.
A high school cultural festival!
What could be better?
So many young people
all in one place,
doing young people things!
[KOU]
Over here, Sonobe.
Come and look at my stand!
[SHINO]
Save me.
Thanks, but I'm
actually pretty full.
I'm just serving juice today,
so you should be fine!
Well, if it's just juice...
Let's see...
[KOU] I can recommend
something if you want.
How about vegetable juice?
You look like a vegetable
juice kinda lady to me.
That sounded vaguely
like an insult.
[KOU] Here, an extra-large
for you, on the house.
Wow, that certainly
is a full glass.
Since you'll probably
see Teru before I will,
do me a favor.
Take a glass of this with you
for her if you don't mind.
[SHINO groans]
Is this supposed to
be some sort of test
of my serving skills?
I must do well in honor
of my former profession.
[KOU giggles] And these two
are for Yoko and Futaba.
[SHINO]
Don't spill!
[BOYS laughing]
Um, you gonna be okay?
[FUTABA]
Never again.
Haunted houses are evil.
I'm never, ever going
in one of them again!
I guess this is your
fault for having
way too good of a costume.
I didn't mean to
scare you so badly.
[FUTABA]
Ah!
Get your creepy zombie face
away from me right now!
[SASAME giggles]
I've never heard
anyone scream like that!
Are you really that scared
of a haunted house?
Hey, stop!
I'm a scary, scary ghost!
Quick, you better
run away from me!
Such a cute widdle ghostie!
I'm not cute! I'm terrifying!
Run away! It approaches!
Do you see?
[YAMAJI] The withered remains of
what used to be a young girl!
Let's get out of here!
[ALL scream]
Hey wait... Come back.
Where are you going?
It's just juice.
[SAKURA]
♪ Sakura! What a pretty girl! ♪
♪ The prettiest in the world! ♪
♪ With a voice so sweet,
no one can compete! ♪
♪ The best you'll
ever meet! Sakura! ♪
[ANNOUNCEMENT 9A] Please be
sure to dispose of trash
and recycling in the
appropriate containers.
Those students who
finish cleaning first
will be dismissed first.
Done! That's it for
this year's festival.
I think it's cool
the curry shop
and the haunted house
were both so successful.
It's definitely an experience
that I'll remember
for a long time.
At first I was worried that
I wouldn't do a good job.
I thought the most
important thing
was a convincing
costume and makeup.
But in the end,
what really mattered
is that everyone
had a lot of fun.
Including me.
It was a great festival!
It really was!
Best ever!
Agreed!
[FUTABA]
Yoko, I was just wondering.
[YOKO]
Yes?
[FUTABA] When are you going
to take that makeup off?
[YOKO] I was just going
to wait until I got home.
[FUTABA]
You should take it off now!
If a kid saw you,
they could be traumatized!
Think of the children,
Miss Yoko!
Think of the children!
[YOKO]
Yes, I have it every day.
I used to be worried
about my dry hair.
[FUTABA] Everything
changed after I drank it!
The world became brighter.
[HAYAMA]
It cleansed my ugly heart.
[KOU] These are some
of the great things
that people are saying about it.