Fall's special.
I eat like five times as much.
What challenge are you
here to compete in today?
Futaba Odagiri!
[SASAME]
You stay away from me!
Big jerkface!
[YOKO]
What is going on here?
I've been given a gift.
Is that so wrong?
It's starting to feel
like fall, isn't it?
It's definitely getting
a lot cooler out these days.
The fall means grapes.
And chestnuts!
And mushrooms!
And pretty, pretty maple leaves!
Huh? What good
are maple leaves?
I mean, really,
what's the point?
Are they even edible?
I don't know if
they taste good,
but you could probably eat them
if you were desperate enough.
Ah! Fall is the ultimate
eating season.
Correct me if I'm wrong,
but aren't they all technically
"eating seasons"?
Fall's special.
I eat like five times as much.
And what about you two?
What kind of season
is it for you?
The season of reading?
The season of thriftiness!
So we're all basically
the same year-round, huh?
Yeah, we are
pretty predictable.
Futaba Odagiri!
Huh?
Okay, well, that was weird.
[HAYAMA] Any idea why that
boy was yelling at you?
It was kind of scary.
Do you know him?
Nope, never seen him before.
What right does a
complete stranger have
to yell at you like that?
His behavior was
worse than rude.
It was threatening.
As your friend,
I won't stand for this!
It's my duty to protect you,
and that's what I'll do.
I'll find him and make him pay!
There's no need to hurt anybody.
Especially since
he's just a kid.
I don't think he is a kid.
He was wearing
East High's uniform.
[FUTABA]
No way! He's in high school?
I thought he was
like 12 or something.
But... You're right.
It was pretty freaky the way
he screamed my full name.
I wonder how he knows who I am.
[SHOP OWNER] All right,
here you are young lady.
[FUTABA squeals]
[SHOP OWNER] Your very own
bucket of almond jelly.
Enjoy.
Aw, yeah!
Like a train wreck.
Totally horrifying,
but you just can't look away.
There's no way you're
gonna pull this one off!
Sorry kid!
I'm down for a refill
if you've got more!
No! You beat me again?
Of course, because
she's a freak of nature.
Way to go, girl!
That was amazing.
So amazing that I
kind of want to vomit.
I didn't realize you'd
done so many challenges.
You really are gonna
put him out of business
if you're not careful.
It's not just this place.
I do challenges
at other shops, too.
Oh, yeah?
[SHOP OWNER]
You know the drill.
We need a photo
to put up on the wall.
Say "bucket of jelly."
Okay! Ready?
Bucket of jelly!
[laughs]
It doesn't matter
how cute and dainty
she looks on the outside.
That girl just slurped down
a whole bucket of jelly.
--[FUTABA] Here, how's this?
--[SHOP OWNER] Good.
[HAYAMA] And there's a wall of
photos with her name on them.
[FUTABA]
That's right. My name.
It makes sense, doesn't it?
That guy could've
learned my name
by looking at the photos
on the restaurant wall.
But that doesn't explain
what he was so mad about.
Yeah, you're right.
Maybe it was the crazed
adoration of a die-hard fan.
Uh... I'm gonna go
with no on that one.
Futaba Odagiri!
I'm not crazy...
You saw that, right?
I think it was
a girl this time.
[YOKO]
It's happened twice now?
That's it! He really
is going to pay!
[FUTABA] It was a different
person this time.
It was a different
person, right?
Like I said,
I think it was a girl.
They did look almost
exactly alike, though.
[FUTABA] I don't get it.
Why would he dress like a girl?
[YOKO]
What is going on here?
Maybe I should get
Yamaji to look into it.
I want some answers!
[SASAME gasps]
Oh, whoops! I'm sorry.
[SASAME]
No, it's my fault.
I wasn't paying attention.
[YOKO]
Hey! Wait a second.
She looks familiar.
This must be the girl Futaba and
Hayama were talking about!
[SASAME]
What's wrong?
Why is she staring at me?
You--! You know what?
I want to talk to you later.
Will you meet me after school?
Huh?
[SASAME]
Well, I'm here.
I wonder what she
wants to talk about.
Nishikawa!
She's so pretty, and smart,
and athletic, and confident.
I think she's amazing!
I've always been too
scared to go up to her,
but now she wants to talk to me!
[FUTABA]
Yep, that's her all right.
Wow.
She really does just
look like him in a skirt.
I know, It's almost like
they're twins or something.
[FUTABA] Think she's
gonna yell at us again?
Sasame Tsuji from Class 2.
Does that sound
right to you, Yoko?
There are a lot of
people in my class,
so it's kinda hard for me to
know everybody's name.
I mean, I haven't had a
chance to talk to all of them.
You said you wanted
to talk, so I came.
But why'd you
bring her with you?
'Cause we're friends.
Is that a problem?
[SASAME]
What?
[SASAME] I finally had a
chance to talk to Nishikawa,
and now she's ruined it!
I'm glad you're here!
There's something I want to
say to you, Futaba Odagiri!
Stay out of my brother's way,
or you'll answer to me!
That guy's your brother?
I called it. They are twins.
Why do people always say that?
He's a year older than me!
[FUTABA]
Are you sure?
[YOKO]
You're basically identical.
[FUTABA]
But how am I in his way?
I didn't do anything.
Oh yes, you did!
Or have you forgotten all the
food challenges you've entered?
So that's what all
this fuss is about.
Your brother's a gluttonous
pig just like Futaba?
He's tried the Stuffed Hut
challenges so many times.
But it's no use.
All he ever wins from
them is a stomachache.
That's gotta be tough.
He's stubborn, and he
hates losing so much.
I know he'll keep trying,
which means he'll keep
making himself sick.
[FUTABA]
Don't worry.
He'll stop entering challenges.
I'm gonna beat him
till he gives up!
[chuckles]
You stay away from me!
Big jerkface!
[whining]
I just love to eat.
It's not like I'm
trying to hurt anybody.
I've been given a gift.
Is that so wrong?
Somebody better
call the wahhmbulance.
[FUTABA]
Maybe I overdid it.
But regular portions
aren't enough for me.
And besides, I'm dead broke.
[SHOP OWNER]
Welcome to the Stuffed Hut!
Ah, Futaba! Is that you?
What challenge are you
here to compete in today?
You're not kicking me out?
I'll just eat something
normal, Mr. Stuffed.
I don't wanna risk being
banned from here too.
Really? Are you sure?
[FUTABA]
Yep.
I'll have a large curry
topped with egg, corn,
cheese, onions, potatoes,
croquette, sausage,
and chicken cutlet please.
[HAJIME]
That's not normal!
It's a Tsuji.
The boy this time.
[HAJIME]
Mister!
I'll have the same thing
as Futaba Odagiri.
Oh yeah. I'm not
giving up, you got that?
I'm gonna take you
down if it kills me!
[SHOP OWNER]
All right, kids. Here ya go.
Thanks, it looks totally yummy!
Okay. I can do this.
Mmm! Delicious!
[HAJIME] I have to win.
I can't let her beat me!
I did it!
I beat her! I beat her!
I'm the champion!
[laughing]
I finished faster than you,
which means I'm the winner
and you're the loser.
So how does failure taste?
Hey, Mr. Stuffed,
the curry tastes different.
Did you change up your recipe?
[SHOP OWNER]
I knew you'd be able to tell!
I tweaked the spice
ratios a little bit.
Don't you get it?
I finished first!
[FUTABA]
There's no point rushing through
a delicious curry if
it's not a competition.
I'd rather take my time and
savor every single bite.
[HAJIME]
Big jerkface!
I'll remember this!
One of these days
I'm gonna beat you!
[SASAME]
I won't forgive you for this!
I hate you, Futaba Odagiri!
[SASAME]
She's here!
[KOU]
Teru!
Hey, Sis, what's up?
Nothing, really.
Just thought I'd walk with you.
[SASAME]
I wonder what she's up to.
If they're going to a shop so
she can do a food challenge,
I have to find
a way to stop her!
Except, if I get in their way,
Nishikawa might get mad.
Then she wouldn't
like me anymore.
Uh... What should I do?
[KOU] Ah. So that boy's into
food challenges, too?
How's it feel to have a rival?
I only do them for the food,
so it's a one sided rivalry.
I don't know if she
could beat Futaba,
but my sister eats a lot too.
Does she do it competitively?
[HAYAMA] No, but ya know
how she's kind of spacey?
She'll completely
zone out and keep eating
without realizing it.
It's pretty amazing, actually.
She can eat her way
through several courses
before finally
noticing she's full.
She's that spacey? Wow.
You feel that?
[ALL]
Hm?
[KOU]
Someone's... watching.
Over there!
I'm sorry, ladies.
I didn't mean to intrude.
[screaming]
Oh, hey there, Yamaji.
Just when you thought
he couldn't get creepier.
Can't you just say hello
like a normal person?
That's weird. I must've
been imagining things.
I thought there was
someone ahead of us,
but I guess it was just Yamaji.
And thanks to my
super stealth skills,
you didn't know where
I was coming from.
Yeah, you're a real ninja.
Can we get going now?
The heck is that?
[FUTABA]
One, two, three!
[SASAME grunts]
That hurt...
Hey, that's Tsuji.
The sister of the boy
who keeps losing to Futaba?
I thought I had you!
How did you know
that it was a trap?
[FUTABA]
Are you serious?
Come on, who would fall
for something like that?
This isn't a cartoon, y'know.
But I catch my brother
like this all the time!
Hey, now...
I'd appreciate it if you
wouldn't compare me to him.
I knew that I
needed to find a way
to keep you from
competing in any more
big-eater challenges.
But I didn't want
Nishikawa to get mad at me,
so I tried to do it without
revealing my identity.
Obviously, that worked
out pretty well didn't it?
I can't believe anybody
would stoop so low
as to try to trap a person
like a common animal!
It is completely despicable!
[SASAME gasps]
[SASAME] This is all your
fault, Futaba Odagiri!
Well those two sure are
good at running away.
Setting a trap like that
takes planning.
Futaba, you have to
be extremely careful!
She may be trying to kill you!
I think I'll take my chances.
Maybe you should've been
nicer to her, though.
But what does that have
to do with anything?
Well, no offense, but...
You don't seem like you're
the most popular girl
in your class, so you
might wanna consider
actually talking to some
of the other students.
She has a valid point.
I've never seen you talk to
anyone else in your class,
and believe me,
I've been watching.
You can come off as
aloof and condescending,
and your classmates
tend to avoid you,
so maybe you shouldn't
make an enemy
of the one person
who actually likes you.
[YOKO]
Yamaji!
[HAYAMA] Tsuji's brother
doesn't seem like
he's giving up anytime soon.
Which means we'll probably
be seeing a lot of him
till he finally wins something.
I'll take care of it.
I'm gonna beat him so bad
he'll never think about
entering another
eating competition.
[HAYAMA] Yeah, that's
one way to handle it.
Or maybe you could try
making friends with him
instead of breaking his spirit.
You already know you have
something in common.
Eh, I dunno. He really
seems to hate me.
Can you two chatterboxes
keep it down?
Some of us here are
trying to read, you know.
[FUTABA]
Sure, sorry about that.
Didn't mean to
interrupt your studying.
What class is this for?
Uh...
Can I have my book back?
[FUTABA] So this is the
kinda thing you like?
Doesn't exactly fit your image.
It isn't mine.
I borrowed it from somebody.
[KONDO]
Oh, hey, Nishiyama.
Is that the book I lent you?
See, it's just like I said.
She always insists on
borrowing my copies.
We've both been huge
fans of the series
ever since elementary school,
but she tends to get
a little obsessive
when a new one comes out!
You can stop talking now!
[HAYAMA]
It's all right.
We all have our
own guilty pleasures.
No one's judging you.
[NISHIYAMA] I'll wipe that
smirk off your stupid face!
[HAYAMA]
No, it's fine!
Don't be embarrassed.
It's cute and fun and simple.
These days, plenty of people
don't even read at all.
Why are you so mean?!
Is it just me, or is there
a lot of that going on lately?
You'd see less of it if you
were nicer to Tsuji's brother.
Or do you like when
people run away from you
screaming and crying?
If you're telling me to
be nice, I've got problems.
[HAYAMA]
Well, no offense, but...
You don't seem like you're the
most popular girl in your class,
so you might wanna
consider actually talking
to some of the other students .
[YOKO] That's true, but how
am I supposed to be nice to her
after the way she's
treated Futaba?
[YOKO]
Oops. Excuse me.
[gasps]
Um... I'm sorry.
I should watch where I'm going.
I'll leave now!
[CAT screeches]
[SASAME yelps]
Are you all right?
That looked like it hurt.
[SASAME]
Yeah, it kinda did.
Oh! My purse spilled.
It's okay, I'll help you.
Here we go.
There are some more over here.
That's really nice of you.
[SASAME]
Aw, looks like I'm 10 yen short.
Guess I'll have to skip
the strawberry milk today.
No!
We won't stop looking
until we find it!
It's okay.
It's not that big of
a deal; just 10 yen.
Excuse me!
Did you say "just 10 yen"?
I'm sorry! I take it back!
[HAYAMA]
Oh. Hey, Yoko.
What are you doing?
You're that other friend
of Futaba Odagiri's.
What's your name?
It's Hayama. I'm in Class 3.
Tsuji fell and
dropped all her coins.
I'm helping her find them.
Did you drop them around here?
[SASAME]
I can't believe this!
I'm surrounded
by Futaba's friends.
How did this happen?
What do I do?
Was it a lot of money?
Yes. I feel awful.
She's still missing 10 yen.
Ten yen?
[HAYAMA]
Here.
Go ahead, take it.
And don't worry
about paying me back.
Ten yen isn't exactly
going to break the bank.
[HAYAMA]
See ya!
I'm really sorry.
I hope you enjoy your
strawberry milk.
Um, thank you.
[SASAME]
Great, now what?
I don't want to be in debt
to one of her friends.
Still, at least I got to talk
to Nishikawa for a little bit.
And Hayama, too.
She seemed nice.
[SASAME] I'm just gonna
give this back to her.
[FUTABA]
Yeah. That's classic Yoko.
She had that look on her face.
You know, the super
serious one she gets
when money's involved?
I know exactly what kinda
look you're talking about.
Honestly, I'm surprised
she hasn't loosened up
about money yet since
she's been working
for quite some time.
[SASAME]
Nishikawa has a job?
[HAYAMA]
Huh?
Tsuji alert.
She doesn't seem like
the type who'd work.
What kind of place is it?
She works at a
cake shop over in
the Central Shopping Arcade.
It's a little place
called Secret Garden.
You've probably seen the fliers.
Oh.
I should quit stalling
and just go in.
[SASAME]
Oh, wow! That is so cool!
A girl in a maid's uniform!
And there's a butler too?
It makes sense.
This place would have
to be pretty high class
for Nishikawa to work here.
--[YOKO] Tsuji?
--[SASAME gasps]
Didn't think you'd
come this quickly.
I was just in the area.
There's no time for excuses!
Let's go in already!
So, uh...
Ah! Smells good.
I've been waiting
all day for this!
I haven't eaten practically
anything for hours.
[SASAME]
This is so weird...
How did this happen?
I'm at a tea party
with Futaba Odagiri!
Have you tried it yet?
Go on, drink while it's hot.
Yeah, it smells wonderful.
And it tastes delicious!
You like it, then? Good!
We carry a lot of teas,
but this is my favorite.
I see why.
The rest of your order is ready.
[FUTABA]
Hand 'em over!
The whole reason
we're here is to try out
the new cake on the menu!
Whoa, did you order
one for me, too?
Why, what's the problem?
Don't you like cake?
Dibs on her piece!
No! I'll eat it! I'll eat it!
[FUTABA]
It's okay. You don't have to.
I want to!
[FUTABA]
Really?
[SHINO] I'm very happy
for you, Miss Yoko.
You've made friends with
another of your schoolmates.
Open up!
[YOKO]
Friends? I don't know.
We haven't known
each other long,
so it's hard to say.
[YAMAJI] It was a miracle just
to have Hayama and Futaba.
Now this?
[SHINO] Having another
high school girl around
will make the shop
feel even more youthful.
I'm quite excited about it.
[YAMAJI] Isn't it nice to
know you can make friends
without buying them?
[SHINO] It's a good
thing you're poor now.
People like you a lot
better than when you were
rich and snobby.
[YOKO] Hey! I don't
have to listen to this!
Be quiet, both of you!
[YOKO] I can't believe Tsuji
actually came to visit the shop.
[STUDENT 1V] I think I'm gonna
see a movie this weekend.
[YOKO] Are they right?
Is she my friend?
I don't know. How do you figure
out something like that?
[whistle]
[P.E. TEACHER] All right.
Let's partner up, everybody!
I have to find a partner!
[SASAME]
Hey, Nishikawa!
[YOKO] Wait, did she
just say my name?
Nobody ever wants
to team up with me.
I'm always the
last person picked.
Half the time I just
end up with the teacher.
Does she really
want to be my partner?
Um, do you...
Are you sure we're
doing this right?
[YOKO yells]
[SHINO] Now, next week's Three
Leaves Three Colors will be:
[SASAME]
It's Sasame. Um...
Oh, next time will
be these three:
"The Cursed Sword, Place of
Death, and Red Spider Lily."
[SHINO]
Rock, paper, scissors!
[chuckling]