What could be
better than a day
to gorge on chicken and cake?
[HAYAMA]
You've been acting weird.
And I want to know the reason.
[KOU giggling]
You are amazing in
every way, Miss Yoko.
Why would anybody put
a cat in a swimming pool?
[DAUGHTER 10A] Look at that
tree, Mommy! It's so pretty!
[MOTHER 10A]
It sure is!
I thought it would
never get here,
but it's finally the season!
Yes, it is, isn't it?
The season of astronomically
high heating bills.
That wasn't really
what I meant.
It has gotten
pretty cold, though.
I could barely bring
myself to get out
from under the
covers this morning.
That gives me an idea!
[FUTABA]
Huh?
[YOKO] I'll wrap myself in
blankets when I'm home
instead of turning up the heat.
That should save a lot of money!
Well, that's one way to do it.
Please, Miss Yoko!
[screams]
[YAMAJI] If you let me
buy you a heater,
then you'll never be cold again!
[WOMAN 10A]
Excuse me.
Oh, I'm sorry about that.
Here you go.
Now, Miss Yoko!
Well, anyway,
what I was trying to
say before was that
Christmas is almost here.
Oh, I guess it is
that season, too.
[FUTABA] Christmas is
very important, y'know.
What could be better than a day
to gorge on chicken and cake?
That's not actually
what Christmas is about.
[FUTABA] Wha--? If it's not
about stuffing your face,
then why does everyone do it?
I guess these days it is mostly
about chicken and cake, huh?
[FUTABA] Hey, whaddaya
think about throwing
our very own Christmas party?
That sounds like
a fantastic idea!
Yay!
We're gonna need a lot of
chicken and a lot of cake!
[YOKO] It takes more than
chicken and cake
to throw a good party.
A Christmas party. Fun!
[FUTABA]
Yoko, wait up!
Good morning.
I'll walk with you.
Did Hayama go to
school early today?
Yep.
Apparently she had some class
rep duties to take care of.
She sure is busy, huh?
All that sucking up she does...
It takes a lot of effort.
Anyway, I've been thinking
about the Christmas party.
I decided that I'm
gonna bake the cake.
Great! Sounds perfect!
[FUTABA]
We'll have it at your place,
and Hayama will be
in charge of snacks.
It's gonna be so much fun!
[KOU giggling]
Did I just overhear you girls
talking about Christmas plans?
Yeah. The three of us
decided to have a little party.
I have some information
you might be interested in.
The 25th is a big day.
It's not just Christmas.
It's also my sister's birthday!
[YOKO, FUTABA]
What?!
What's up with you two?
You're acting kinda funny.
[overlapping chatter]
[YOKO] I can't believe
that Hayama's birthday
is on Christmas.
[FUTABA]
Wait, so that means...
[HAYAMA laughs evilly]
[FUTABA] A demon was
born on a holy day!
[YOKO]
Such a contradictory occurrence.
[overlapping chatter]
[HAYAMA] What are you
even talking about?!
[HAYAMA]
You've been acting weird.
And I want to know the reason.
[BOTH gasp]
[FUTABA]
We have to go.
Earlier, Yoko said there's
something she needed
to discuss with me
and nobody else.
What? I didn't say
anything like that.
[FUTABA]
Sure ya did. Come on!
[YOKO] Wait, will you at least
tell me where we're going?
We need to get a grip or she's
gonna know that something's up.
She's really suspicious.
What do you think we should do
about the Christmas party?
Hey, I know!
We'll still have a party,
only now it'll be a
birthday party for Hayama.
[YOKO] Huh?
How will that work, exactly?
We'll keep planning, and
whenever we talk to her,
we'll act like it's for
the Christmas party.
Think how surprised she'll
be when she finds out
it's actually for her birthday!
Oh!
So we're going to set
a trap and ambush her?
Not really how I'd put it.
The important thing to remember
is to keep it a secret
from Hayama.
I won't breathe
a word to her.
[ALL gasp]
Where did you come from,
and what are you doing here?
[SHINO] I'm passing out flyers
for Christmas cakes.
[YOKO] I thought I told you not
to do that here anymore.
[SHINO] Are you sure?
That's a shame.
If our sales were to go up,
I might be able
to afford to give you a raise.
I refuse to be tempted.
You and your flyers
will leave at once!
Cake shops must be
busy this time of year,
what with all the parties.
We have been
working quite hard.
On top of normal business,
there are orders
for specialty cakes
and holiday pastries,
so we've been baking nonstop.
Wait, "we"?
Do you mean you actually
help with the baking?
I measure out ingredients
and sprinkle things on top.
She is an expert sprinkler.
I don't know how I would
survive the busy holiday season
without her assistance.
You look so shocked,
but as you can see,
my help is essential.
You are amazing in
every way, Miss Yoko.
So, we done with
this conversation yet?
Hold on...
If you're so vital
to the cake shop,
does that mean you'll have
to work on Christmas?
I give you permission
to take the day off.
After a life of loneliness,
you finally have friends.
I will work from dawn
until dusk without rest,
so you may celebrate
your friend's birthday.
Thank you so much!
Despite her lack
of experience,
she's somehow
slightly more useful
than a cat in a swimming pool.
You'll make me blush!
'Kay, seriously.
Can we be done now?
[HAYAMA]
Hold on just one minute!
Why would anybody put
a cat in a swimming pool?
Oh, we didn't see you there!
Whatcha doin'?
[HAYAMA] I want to know
what the two of you
have to say that I'm
not allowed to hear.
I must confess.
We have been keeping
a secret from you.
Uh, Sonobe...
I hope you can handle it.
The truth is I'm planning to
add bear and cat-shaped cakes
to the shop menu
sometime in the near future.
[FUTABA, YOKO]
What?
How cute!
[SHINO] I asked the others
to keep it a secret
because I wanted
to surprise you.
[HAYAMA] Aww! I'm sorry
I spoiled the surprise!
I can't wait to see 'em!
That maid's more
useful than she looks.
We owe Sonobe for
getting us out of that one.
[NISHIYAMA]
I love Christmastime.
The streets are so pretty,
and people look so happy.
And it's so much fun
to pick out presents!
[NISHIYAMA] I wonder which
one would look better.
Pink's nice, but the red
one's really pretty, too.
[chuckles]
[NISHIYAMA] I spent an hour
deciding and wound up
getting both.
It cost my whole allowance,
but I don't care.
My sweet Eternal
is worth twice that!
Things are really starting
to come together, aren't they?
Yes, and I'm very excited.
I've never had the chance
to throw a birthday party
for a friend before!
[FUTABA] We have to make sure
it's the best party ever.
Since it's Christmas and
Hayama's birthday.
Hey, hold on a sec!
[FUTABA]
What's up, Nishiyama?
What was that about just now?
You were saying something
about Hayama's birthday.
[FUTABA]
Oh, you heard that, did ya?
We were talking about
Hayama's birthday
and the fact that it
falls on Christmas.
We're throwing her a party,
but it's a surprise,
so don't say anything
about it, okay?
[YOKO]
We appreciate it.
[BOY 10A]
Okay!
Will you tell him that I
want a bike and a video game...
[NISHIYAMA]
No, that's too crazy.
[KONDO humming "Jingle Bells"]
[KONDO]
Nishiyama?
Why are you sitting
down there?
It's almost Christmas.
Best day of the year.
Yeah.
I know how much you
like Christmas,
so I thought that
this year, maybe--
[NISHIYAMA]
I don't care.
[KONDO]
Huh?
[NISHIYAMA]
It's not special.
Just another day.
What's gotten into you?
You're always so happy
this time of year!
Maybe a Christmas party
will cheer you up!
[NISHIYAMA]
No, thanks.
I think I'll just get
some take-out instead.
Maybe a nice curry or something.
No way!
I don't know what
your problem is,
but you and I are having
a Christmas party!
Now come on, get up!
Stop being such a grump and
let's go pick out a cake
for our party.
[HAYAMA] I'm taking off!
See you later!
[KOU]
Hold on a sec.
I've got something for you.
[KOU giggles]
You are gonna love this!
I spent all night making this
special stew for your party!
[HAYAMA]
Special, or scary?
[KOU] I hope you three
have fun tonight!
I can't decide. Where do
you think should I put this?
Anywhere, just pick a place.
She's gonna be here
any minute now.
[doorbell rings]
[BOTH]
Okay!
--Hey, I'm here!
--[FUTABA] Hayama!
Merry Christmas!
And happy birthday!
Wow, that was terrifying!
I really thought you
were gonna shoot me!
Of course not!
You're mean sometimes, but
we wouldn't shoot you for it!
[HAYAMA]
Ah...
I guess my sister
must have told you.
I didn't mention it
'cause I didn't want you
to feel obligated
to do anything.
[YOKO]
It's not about obligation!
[HAYAMA]
I usually just celebrate it
along with Christmas anyway,
so I'm used to my
birthday being secondary.
It's no big deal.
That's kinda sad, actually.
Thanks for this, though.
It's been years since
I've had a birthday party
with more than just family.
[YOKO laughs]
Want some cake?
I baked it myself!
Sounds yummy, thanks.
I helped out by
measuring ingredients
and sprinkling things on top.
Well it looks
expertly sprinkled.
I almost forgot, I brought
something with me, too.
My sister made this.
I can't let food go to waste!
[FUTABA]
Whoa!
We don't know
that it is food!
[YOKO gagging]
[HAYAMA]
Uh...
Um, maybe you should stop.
[FUTABA]
You can do it, Yoko!
[HAYAMA]
Are you okay?
Oh my, how amazing!
I almost feel like I could
run a marathon right now!
Should we call a doctor?
[HAYAMA] I guess I
shouldn't have brought it.
Whoops.
[NISHIYAMA]
Ugh.
[KONDO]
Ya know, at some point,
you're gonna have
to let this go.
It's like some sort
of cruel joke.
How can Christmas be my
favorite day of the year
if it's her birthday?
[HAYAMA laughs]
Was your Christmas
festive and full of joy?
[NISHIYAMA]
Go away!
You know it's also the day I was
brought into the world, right?
I want you to apologize to
Christmas right this instant!
I don't see why
I should do that.
When the streets are
decorated so prettily
to celebrate my advent.
You're horrible!
You're a nasty,
evil Christmas-ruiner!
I hate you so much,
Hayama! I hate you!
[HAYAMA laughs]
Peace on Earth.
[BEELZEBUB meows]
[YOKO] I can't believe how
much has piled up already.
It's only the first
snow of the winter.
[YAMAJI]
Yeah, it is unusual.
I find the feel of
freshly fallen snow
to be invigorating.
[YOKO] Invigorating or not,
we can't open the shop
until it's all cleared away.
[SHINO sighs]
I suppose you're right.
It's freezing out here.
And my back's starting to hurt.
[YAMAJI]
Miss Yoko is too delicate.
She shouldn't be
forced to shovel snow.
I bet this is your fault!
You made it snow, didn't you?
[SHINO] You've accused me
of a lot of things,
but that's a new one.
[YOKO]
It doesn't seem to be stopping.
You're right, it doesn't.
Won't we be slow?
I can't imagine that many people
will want to come out
in this weather.
[SHINO]
That's not necessarily true.
It's a known fact that many
people love blizzards
and will be more eager than
normal to venture out.
[YOKO]
Really? I've never heard that.
[door opens]
Hey, everybody!
[SHINO]
See?
Honestly, I'm surprised even
you came on a day like today.
[FUTABA]
Well...
I was lookin' outside
at the snow,
and it gave me the
strongest craving for cake.
[YOKO] So, something with
whipped cream for you, then?
[FUTABA]
Tiramisu, chocolate ganache,
and opera cake please!
Were you looking at snow
or at the mud puddles
left behind after
it's melted away?
[KOU]
Hey, Teru!
It's snowing like crazy!
Let's go outside and play!
Not a chance.
[KOU gasps]
But we can't let a
beautiful blanket of snow
go to waste, can we?
The best way to spend
a cold, snowy day
is inside with a warm,
snuggly cat on your lap.
[KOU]
Oh, come on!
Let's go. Just for a little,
I promise! It'll be fun!
[HAYAMA]
No! I don't wanna!
[BEELZEBUB meows]
[KOU] Ta-da!
Check out the igloo I made!
[HAYAMA]
Wow!
Were you out here
all night or something?
[KOU]
Isn't it amazing?
And it's even warm inside, too.
Go on, see what it's like!
I'll be back in a second.
I'm going to get us
something hot to drink.
She wasn't lying.
It is warm in here.
[HAYAMA]
How strange.
Who knew that snow could
hold in so much warmth?
[KOU]
Uh-oh!
[FUTABA laughs]
[phone chimes]
Oh no!
It looks like Hayama got buried
in some kind of avalanche!
Is she okay?
[HAYAMA shivering]
This is what happens when
you go outside on a snow day.
[FUTABA]
Teru, hey!
You wanna come out and play?
You wanna come out and... play?
What do you want?!
Just checkin' in on you.
I got a message saying
that you were in trouble.
[HAYAMA] There's this
thing called a doorbell.
[YOKO] I can't believe
it still hasn't stopped.
Seriously.
It looks like it's gonna
snow the rest of the year.
So what are you
doing for New Year's?
Any big plans?
I don't know if
I'll do anything.
[HAYAMA] You mean you're
gonna be spending it alone?
Yes.
Unacceptable!
I will not allow it!
[YOKO] I don't have
anyone to spend it with.
It's just an idea,
but why don't the three
of you do something?
[SHINO]
That is, of course,
assuming that Hayama and
Futaba would be interested.
Sounds good to me.
You can count me in, too.
New Year's is more fun if
you spend it with friends.
Thank you both so much!
[YAMAJI yells]
With that decided, I suggest
you have a pajama party.
[YOKO]
But what's... that?
Something that girls do.
Similar to a rite of passage.
A recent study on the
prevalence of pajama parties
revealed that more
than 80% of all girls
will have attended
at least one by the time
they graduate high school.
I know you just made that up.
But perhaps you're
intimidated by the thought
of hosting such an
important gathering.
[YOKO] Nothing intimidates
a Nishikawa daughter!
I will host a pajama party, and
I will do it in grand fashion!
Is that all right with you two?
Sure.
That sounds a good time to me.
Then we will need
decorations, hor d'oeuvres,
and of course a tiered cake
to mark the occasion.
Actually, pajama parties tend
to be a little more relaxed.
We basically just
hang out in bed
wearing pj's and
talk about stuff.
That's not like any kind
of party I've ever heard of.
[HAYAMA]
We need a lot of blankets.
Do you think you have
enough at your place,
or should we bring some
with us when we come over?
Um, blankets...?
I don't know.
We all have blankets.
What are we supposed to do now?
This is the part
where we're supposed
to talk about being
in love and stuff.
All right. Let's discuss.
I love rice and bread too!
Carbs are the best!
I could eat them forever!
I love cats, and dogs too!
I can't choose between them!
Please don't make me!
[YOKO]
So this is a pajama party?
Oh! I almost forgot.
I brought snacks for us.
Okay! I shall make some tea.
[YOKO yelps]
That looked painful!
Are you okay?
[yelping]
[overlapping chatter]
This is completely unacceptable.
A real pajama party
should involve a lot more
girlish squealing and giggling.
You orchestrated this.
What are you up to?
I'm not up to
anything, thank you.
I simply want Miss Yoko
to have the experiences
any normal girl her age does.
Is that so wrong?
Why are you recording it?
To preserve the memories.
[YAMAJI]
Deranged old hag.
[SHINO]
Creepy stalker.
[YAMAJI]
Well, at least she won't spend
her New Year's alone.
That's what matters.
Wow, I can hardly believe
it's already morning.
It's not just morning.
It's a whole new year.
Happy New Year, Yoko.
Right!
Happy New Year
to you as well, Hayama.
I would say our pajama
party was a success,
wouldn't you?
A total success!
[chopping noise]
Food's almost ready
for ya, girls!
Mama!
Thank you, Mama!
Yes, yes. Anything
for you, my sweetcakes.
Now, get ready to
pound some mochi!
To do what?!
[YOKO]
What's this?
[HAYAMA]
No idea.
It's a mochi pounding machine.
When you said
"pounding mochi,"
I was imagining a mortar
and pestle type situation.
So was I.
Cool, huh? I asked
for it for my birthday.
[HAYAMA, YOKO]
Wow!
And now to eat! Woo!
High school girls enjoying
a post pajama party
breakfast of mochi.
What an extremely rare
and beautiful sight.
[YAMAJI] What have I told
you about recording them?
[SHINO]
It's for preservation!
Yummy!
I think I'm in heaven!
It's delicious,
and so fresh, too!
Yeah!
[FUTABA] Pan-fried with
soy sauce and served
with your choice
of edamame paste,
fermented soy bean
paste, or walnuts!
How many dozens should I make?
--What?
--Did you just say "dozens"?
Mochi's the most important
part of New Year's!
Go on ladies, enjoy yourselves,
go wild, try one!
This is breakfast, not one
of your big-eater challenges.
[overlapping chatter]
[HAYAMA]
Stop it! No more!
[YOKO]
An event in February?
That must be--
[YAMAJI] Yes, the
Festival of Broken Needles!
An event where
a memorial service
is held for broken needles.
It's an event geared
towards women.
[YOKO]
Valenti--
[YAMAJI]
Or the Bean Throwing Festival!