All righty! That's all the time we have.
And just a reminder that the
days are starting to get shorter,
so be sure to get home before the sun sets.
Finally! Let's go, dude!
Behind you, bro!
A bunch of people seem to think plasma is the answer,
but I'm not entirely sure if they're correct.
I prefer gathering evidence...
Hey, Nano!
Ah! Yes?
Wanna walk home together?
We can grab a bite, too!
Whaddaya say?
So? Wanna?
Uh. Well.
Hey! Mio, you should come, too.
Well, poop. It looks like she bailed already.
Anyway.
Weird.
He was like super gross.
I ran into him at the mall when I was getting my coffee...
I can't believe I just did that.
Leaving her alone there was so thoughtless and mean.
Maybe if I'd introduced myself like a normal
girl, it would've been easier to hide in plain sight.
Uh, hi. My name's Nano Shinonome!
And, um, you see, I, uh, I was
on my way to school and then I...
I heard the local coffee shop got remodeled
recently, so I went over to take a peek.
Uh, miss?
Are you ready to order?
Just the espresso. The "T" one.
Um, so, uh,
you would like one espresso in a tall, is that correct?
Wait, in a what? "Tall"?
That's what "T" stands for?
You know what, that T espresso
thing sounds pretty good in a tall.
So, yeah, uh.
Lemme get the T espresso... in a small size?
You wanna order the short espresso instead of the tall?
Uh-huh.
I'll take it in a small short!
That's the one I want!
Um. Sure. So with the espresso order... Uh!
It, uh... You can get it served either hot or cold.
Hot please!
Okay then.
I'll whip that up for you right away.
For size...
...it varies.
You can get a solo or doppio.
D-D-Doppi-what? Doppio?
What the heck is a doppio? Is that even a real word?
How am I supposed to know what that means?
Does it even say it anywhere? What is doppio?
Actually, scratch that, I changed my mind.
I'm just gonna get today's special...
whatever that drink happens to be.
Well, uh.
For today, the special is also the espresso.
Fine then. That one.
Right.
Would that be a solo...
...or a doppio for this order?
Or a doppio? Or a doppio? Or a doppio for this order?
Sure.
I'll take it.
Huh?
I mean, uh...
Just gimme whatever feels right in your heart.
Coming right up then.
Thank you for waiting.
Here's your solo espresso.
It's so tiny.
And so bitter!
Thank you! Please come again!
Welp, I have no choice.
It's vending machines for life.
They'll never judge me.
For my dear grandson's birthday, I
bought him a brand new baseball glove.
Grandpa! Here it comes!
Try your best, my boy!
You're pretty far away, so give it all you've got!
Ah, the young people. Always
so full of excitement and dreams.
You ready?!
Ready as I'll ever be.
Now throw it as hard as you can!
This is the perfect opportunity to
show him how cool his grandpa can be.
Curveball.
Uh, 'scuse me.
Yes?
Can I get one of these Agonizing Super-Hot
Chef's Fanciful Chicken Bars on a stick please?
Seriously? You actually want one of those things?
What's the matter, Koujirou?
Oh, yeah. I gotta hurry before the post offices clo...
Mio!
Oh, it's you. What up?
I was lookin' for ya.
You kinda booked it as soon as homeroom was over, y'know?
Yeah. I guess I did.
Well, it doesn't matter.
Now that we're here, why don't we walk home t...?
I gotta do something.
Really? What?
It's, uh... It's kinda hard to explain.
Ah, come on! It can't be that
hard. You should at least try.
Uh, I just have, um, a thing!
What kind of thing? Is it a...?
Excuse me a moment.
You're a...
I didn't do it!
Wait, what? He didn't ask anything!
Uh! That was just a weird reflex.
I didn't mean to catch you off guard.
And relax, you're not in any trouble.
That's good.
Is there something we can help you with, officer?
Yes, actually.
Some counterfeit bills have been
used in these vending machines.
I was wondering if you've seen
any suspicious activity in the area.
I haven't seen any.
Me neither, but I don't pass by here that often.
Based on an eyewitness report, there was a shady person
carrying a beige tote with red stripes.
Hm.
Nah. There's no way that you could...
Wait.
Why is she actually making that weird, kinda gross face?
Did she actually do it? Is she the culprit?
No way. She would never do that.
Mio. Quit joking around already.
Is she squealing on herself?
She'd never survive in the slammer!
Wait a second.
You aren't the one that did it, are you?
That's crazy talk!
She's just super into volleyball and is
practicing her bumping form or whatever.
Isn't that right?
Okay then.
If it's all right with you two,
I'd like to check inside your bags just in case.
Of course! Go ahead!
Hear that? We...
She whipped it out! She has a real fake bill!
It's all over now! I can't believe my friend's a criminal!
Take this... and please look the other way.
Take the money! And let me go!
Is this one of your counterfeit bills?
No, that's real cash! And it's also a bribe!
That's quite suspicious!
Now show me what's in your
bag! And stop resisting the law!
This bag isn't mine! I swear!
I've never seen it in my life!
You fool.
One, two!
Three! Four!
Five!
Where's six?
Passion.
Huh?
A fever? Silly.
Hm?
What? Huh?
Wait!
Oh, there you are. Don't run off like that.
It's like you're a newborn.
Mio! Are you gonna come and eat?
Food's getting cold!
Hey, Mio! Say something!
"The Life of Koujirou"! Check him out!
Hm?
What are you chewing...? Ah!
There's the bell!
Classes are done for today!
Don't forget that midterms are coming up,
so be sure to study hard.
The test's subjects are on the
board if you need a reminder.
Goodbye!
Nano always books it outta here as soon as she can.
Hmm.
See ya!
See you tomorrow.
Have a good day!
You as well.
When I don't know something,
I just pretend that I do.
♪ Cha-cha-la-la! Cha! ♪
♪ Cha-cha-cha-cha Cha-la-la! ♪
Uh.
Yuuko, can I borrow an eraser?
You may!
Which hand?
Uhh...
Hey, Mai, do you have an eraser?
I do. Here.
A character eraser?
Man, this isn't gonna work.
These just smudge everything.
Yuuko, lend me your eraser.
This is really all you had on you?
Wouldja look at that?
'Kay, which hand?
This one.
Whoa! Wait a sec! That's cheating!
The rules clearly state you have to pick one at a time.
You mean the rules you just made up?
Mai, you first.
Go right ahead. You can zoom in as much as you'd like!
Ah! Zoom out! Zoom out!
What the heck?! You're not allowed to attack the hand!
That'll be a strike for you, Mai.
And that means?
It's a penalty. Duh.
And so what happens when you get a penalty?
Uhh...
You gotta treat me to 23 juices!
You're still hung up on that?
Are ya hungry, Yuuko? Have a snack!
Ready... kan-ji-zai-bo-sa-gyyo-
jin-han-nya-ha-ra- mi-ta-ji-sho-kei-go.
There! Did it!
Man, that was a close one!
It's not sho-kei-go, it's sho-ken-go.
And you were this close to falling for it.
Yeah? Two strikes for you!
Rock-paper-scissors!
Heh. Ha!
Like I would play with the hand that has the eraser in it.
This one.
Dios mio ! I fell for it!
Hand it over. We won fair and square.
Yeah, all right, fine.
Here. Your prize.
More character erasers?
Thank you! Please come again!
Why are there so many character erasers?
Tell me about it. Oh. Isn't that Nano?
Yeah, it is!
She's definitely, probably, maybe a robot.
Would you cut that out already?
It really bothers her, y'know?
Why would it bother her?
Robots are legit!
Gah.
Hey.
Wanna run for it?
What? C'mon, Dad. I don't get it.
Why do you want me to wear this thing in public?
It's like embarrassing!
Ya think so, huh?
Well then... you're just a spineless, mugwort dumpling!
Let's see. Which one is Shinonome?
Ah! This one!
Wait. Shinonome Lab?
Oh! I guess a lab makes sense!
That's awesome!
'Scuse me! Anybody home?
Huh. No answer.
Coming! Be right there!
So sorry to keep you...
Wha...?
Oh, no! How did this happen?
What am I gonna do?
Why did she show up at our front door?
If she somehow gets the chance to meet Hakase,
then my secret'll be out for sure!
Hmm. How should I handle this?
Wait. Hang on.
Maybe she's just here to give
me a print-out I forgot at school.
That would explain why she came all the way out here.
So, this is the hall.
Thank you for the grand tour!
No!
She's already made herself at home.
I'll just have to find out what she
wants before Hakase says anything crazy.
Ugh. I'm starving.
I'm starving. I'm starving.
Hm?
Hey! Who was that?
It was Sakamoto, our talking cat!
Hakase!
For real?
No! Don't be silly! Of course he isn't!
Hey! Meow for me! Now! Do it right meow! Please?
Huh? Why do I have to...?
Please, Sakamoto!
Uh. Meow.
See? He's a normal cat!
Uh. Mh-hm.
All right, kitty, we have a guest here today,
so why don't you go and play outside, 'kay?
You're kicking me out of...?
Fine!
Meow.
I haven't introduced myself to you yet, huh?
I'm Yuuko Aioi!
So, are you Nano's little sister or something?
I'm not a sister. I'm Hakase!
Oh, and I built Nano!
You built her?
Awesome! Small and smart!
I'm just your run-of-the-mill kid genius.
Wait, no! She's just messing around with you!
I actually have some relatives that live nearby,
but they work all the time,
so they drop their daughter off here so I can watch her!
She's here so often, it's like a second home!
Right? Isn't that right? Huh? Huh?
Whatchu talkin' 'bout?
Would you take a hint?!
Uh, please excuse me! I'll go make some more tea!
Ah! No need! I got it!
Well, more like, you got it.
Huh?
There you go!
That is the coolest ever!
And the other hand is a gun.
There's more? That's even cooler!
My life is over.
And next up, we're gonna say a buncha random cool things!
Yay!
Our first contestant is yours truly!
Hey. Open your eyes. Wake up.
Don't you die on me!
Wow. Now that's a cool scene!
Now, Hakase!
Me!
Rhinoceros Beetle!
That's cool!
So... why did she come over anyway?
They're on top of each other!
I give! I give!
You're so tiny!
It's too big!
'Kay. I'mma go.
She came for nothing?
Thanks for having me over.
Sorry I stayed so late.
Uh. No problem.
And, um, I wanted to say.
Yeah?
Truth is, I've actually been
practicing some magic tricks lately!
So I'm not a robot, or anything, I swear!
Yeah, I already knew that.
You're Nano. And that's good enough for me!
There we go.
As long as you're happy with who you are,
that's all that matters.
I just wanted to stop by here and tell you that.
But I got distracted.
See you at school, Nano!
Uh. Yeah.
Hey!
Hm?
Uh.
Come by at any time.
Sure! Sounds fun!
Really? Hooray!
I gotcha! How 'bout we doodle next time?
Yeah! We can draw sharks and stuff!
Oh, I like that! Sharks are cool!
They sure are! They're the best!
You really like those sharks, don'tcha, Hakase?
Not like! I love sharks!
They're the coolest!
Rawr! I'mma shark!
Do more! Do more shark things!
Rawr! Shark attack! Rawr!
Again! Again!
Hakase! I wanna play!
Look out! I'm gonna thrash!
So cool!
Oh, no!
Me shark! Me hungry!
Hi, Sakamoto!
'Kay, bye!
See ya.
Huh, bizarre.
It's me, the screw!
I have a Phillip's head, so that's a plus!
I also give off plenty of positive vibes,
so I'm sure that adds lots to my character!
The next episode of My Ordinary Life is Episode 17.
Look forward to it!