I bet she's a total master at mental math!
Who's a what now?
Nano, the transfer student.
Hm?
A robot like her would have a
calculator function or something, right?
What're you talkin' about?
There's no way that she's a robot.
Come on, it's so obvious with
that thing sticking out of her!
Huh? The key in her back is your only piece of evidence?
You're jumping to conclusions.
Hang on! Just hear me out on this one.
If she is a robot...
...that'd be dope!
And it'd also be off the chain!
I have no idea what that means, but you're sure excited.
I think I'm gonna officially start
investigating to see if Nano is a for-real robot.
Hold on! Isn't that going too far?
It's no prob!
I've come up with a foolproof plan!
Oh, Nano?
Yes?
Question for ya.
Hm?
What's 3,260 plus 260, then divided by 320?
Well, uh, if I were to follow
the order of operations, uh...
It sure is a thinker.
Maybe you should calculate this one.
You're kidding me! That was your big idea?
That's a toughie.
If you don't mind, I'd like to use something special.
A bite!
The line snapped!
'Kay, first things first.
I'll need to start by wiping the slate completely clean.
She's legit using it!
Here goes. One, two, three.
She's like... like a...
...like a... She's a like, a total newb!
All right, take 3,260 and...
What happened to using the abacus?
Wha...?! Hey, pull it together!
What happened to her?
How you holdin' up?
Don't worry 'bout me.
I just crumbled under the weight of my ambitions.
I told you right from the get-go
that she wasn't a robot girl, didn't I?
Any way I can help? I could offer you a drink?
This is it! It's the sacred chalice!
Could it be? Show me the oil!
What a soup-prise!
Yuuko!
Oh, guess not. Huh?
Hey there.
Here.
She threw a fastball!
Oil?
For you.
Oh! That's so nice.
I appreciate the gesture.
Strike!
You can have this, too.
Curveball!
A monkey wrench?!
Wow, thanks a bunch. I needed one of these.
To eat?
Another strike!
All right, you two.
I think now's a good time to chill the heck out.
Can't you see that she's uncomfortable?
It's skinship.
Yeah, we just wanted to be friends with you.
Seriously?
There's no way she'll be your friend
if you keep freaking her out like that!
I'm sorry.
That's better.
Hey! I'm not bothered, so don't worry.
Huh? You sure?
Oh. That's right! The soup!
I'll help myself if no one else wants it.
Would you look at that?
I guess things are all good then!
She's obviously...
Did I lose a tooth?
If you try putting yourself in
her shoes, how would you feel?
Cut it out already.
I need to know.
How did such a highly advanced technology come to be?
That transfer student who just
started here has a strange demeanor.
In addition to that bizarre key.
Well, no matter how you slice it,
she absolutely has to be a robot.
Why was such an innovative
piece of tech being kept secret?
And why is she attending our plain
little high school, of all places?
I want to know. I need to know.
For science.
Once I do, that robot will be mine.
Oh!
Pardon the intrusion, but I brought the
textbooks you asked me to get, Ms. Nakamura.
She came!
Now I must act, posthaste!
All done! If you'll excuse me, I'll be going.
One moment, Miss Shinonome!
So, uh, would you like a cup of coffee before you go?
Huh? No! I would hate to be a bother!
Oh, come on. Don't be such a stick in the mud.
You can think of this as a "thank you."
Here, I just brewed a fresh beaker.
Get it while it's hot.
One cup won't hurt me.
Let's see what happens if I add a
little something to calm her down.
Way down.
For science, of course.
If there are no results, I'll
resort to my trusty Mr. Short Circuit.
Again, for science.
Here ya go.
Thanks so much. It smells really good!
Why'd I drink it?
Fight it.
Hang in there!
Well, uh, I'm gonna head out now.
Wait, come back.
I need to study you... for science.
Hey. Did ya hear?
Ms. Nakamura the science teacher passed out.
Oh, wow, she sure does that a lot, doesn't she?
Rawr! Rawr!
Today was pretty stressful.
There were one too many close calls,
but my classmates seem really nice.
I hope we can all be friends someday.
Take this!
Rocket punch!
Ka-boom!
Taste my robot's maximum power!
Ha-ha!
Hakase! Hakase!
Ah, Nano! Good to have you back!
Huh...? Why did you just say the same thing twice?
Know what, never mind that for right now!
I wanted to ask you to take this key off of me!
Uhh... But why?
What do you mean "why"?
It's negatively impacting my school life!
I can never sit back properly in my chair.
Students look at me weird and one even filmed me!
I've been able to get by so far,
but I don't know if that'll last.
Ahh.
That key's so cute though.
But can't you see that as long
as I have it stuck on my back,
the other kids are never gonna
treat me like a normal girl?
It'll help make you popular!
I wanna be normal!
And I wanna have an ordinary high school life, so...
Huh?
Why? I never asked to have these crazy features.
At least my hand didn't come off at school.
What's the big deal if everyone
finds out that you're a robot?
People will think that I'm not cute
'cause everyone knows that robots aren't cute.
But robots are the cutest!
They're not even the littlest bit cute!
They are!
Is this gun barrel cute?
Yeah, it is!
And what about the USB drive in my big toe?
Adorable!
Even the sweet buns in my forehead?
I said it's cute!
Yeah? I say you're a mad scientist!
I just wanna live an ordinary high school life!
Wow! It's chikuwa !
Those sure are tasty!
Sorry I'm late, fellas.
Three. Two. One.
Four o'clock! Four o'clock!
Four o'clock! Four o'clock! Four o'clock! Four o'clock...
Four o'clock! Four o'clock! Four o'clock...
Hey there! It's me, daifuku !
And I'm cheap! Get your daifuku here!
Mr. Nakanojou! I hope you're doing well!
True daifuku don't talk!
I'm sorry. But I can't help it.
I get so worked up when I wear this mask!
I put my entire heart and soul...
What did I say about speaking?
Okay. Mistakes may have been made.
And I might have taken things
too far, but that's science for you.
I can't underestimate that robot.
It's gonna take all I have to bring her in and study her.
Enter Mr. Short Circuit!
My trusty robot disabling device
that's never failed me 'cause I've never used it!
I'm positive that this'll do the trick.
Or why else would I call it "trusty"?
Time is of the essence.
Run away!
Uh. Ms. Nakamura?
Hold on! What's this?
You need to you fasten that top button of yours, mister!
Would you just leave me alone?
I can have it unbuttoned if I want!
No way! You need to do what your student counselor says!
Ugh. Seriously?
You're playing the counselor card?
Yes, I am. Come here so I can button you.
I can do it myself! Don't embarrass me like that!
Uh...
What's going on?
I can't count on you to fix it,
so I'll just do it for you, Mako.
Hey, back off.
Wait, "Mako"?
Come here.
What are you doing manhandling me like that?
I said back off!
Hold still. I'll fix you up so you can go to class.
"Manhandling"?!
"I'll fix you up"?
Ugh, cut it out.
Hey, just stop groping me would you?
"Groping"?!
What kind of relationship do these two have?
Well, what do ya know, problem solved.
'Kay, see ya. Got places to be.
Hold on a sec!
Aren't you afraid everyone'll make fun of
you for being dressed all sloppy like that?
I'm sloppy?
You're the one who dresses
sloppy at home all the time, y'know?
"At home"? Does she wear a-a sloppy dress?
Sloppy dress at home! Oh, yeah!
Wait, that doesn't make sense!
When would a Chinese dress ever be considered sloppy?
Am I dumb or something?
How could I possibly be a teacher and be this stupid?
I've gotta pull myself together!
Think! What's counts as being sloppy in a normal sense?
Dressing like this?
Enough! Stop it! You idiot!
Are you finished? I'm outta here.
You didn't fix your button!
"The Life of Oguri Cap!" Check him out!
You idiot!
Are you finished? I'm outta here.
You didn't fix your button!
I've gotta follow.
Mr. Takasaki!
We found Nakanojou unconscious
on the floor of the science room!
Wha...?
We need you to come help like, right now!
Hey, wait a second!
Leave me alone!
Okay. Now listen up.
Yeah?
I'm sure Nakanojou's fine!
Huh?!
That's right! He's probably just napping!
But I looked at his eyes and they're all whited out!
Wha...?
Fill them in.
Huh?
I'll give it a shot.
Wha...?
Don't do that!
Huh?
Look over there!
Give me the lowdown on this business!
It's my sworn duty as a teacher to
stop this kind of illicit relationship.
It's more important than, uh, you know.
Get what I mean?
You mean Ms. Sakurai and her little brother over there?
Let's go.
'Kay?
Prepare yourself.
There's no time to waste.
After all, I am a teacher.
Hey, it's this way!
Hop! Hop! H...
Hop!
Next stop: Tokisadame Station, North Gate.
A stop has been requested.
That's not even close to your stop, dude!
Yeah, but it's so fun to push the buttons every time!
You pushed the last one too, right?
And no one even noticed
'cause someone had to get off anyway!
So I guess you're actually helpin' 'em out then!
Oh, look! Someone needed to get off again!
Hey, you're welcome!
Mom, where'd we put the daily
calendar with all those tear-off pages?
It should be in the closet, I think.
Hakase! Hakase!
Ah, Nano! Good to have you back!
Listen! I think it's about time
to take this key off of my back!
It's starting to cause more and more
problems in my daily school activities!
We did the high jump in gym class
today, and I could only belly roll over it!
And during soccer, I got put on the
bench because I fouled a kid with my key.
Okay. I can take it.
Splat!
If you were so willing, you should've told me earlier.
I gotcha. I'll take it right now if you want.
Not a day goes by that I don't
wish to have this thing off my body.
But now, I can finally start my
new life as a normal high school girl!
If you don't mind, I'd like to
get this key taken right away.
Cheese.
Hakase? Don't tell me you're...
I took it.
Plop!
I feel betrayed.
Why?
I thought you meant you were gonna remove my key,
not take a picture of it!
Oops, my bad.
So, are you ever gonna take off my key for real?
Let's see.
Hmm...
Kapow!
I've had it up to here with your silly gags!
Will you do it? Or will you not do it?
Calm down. I can do it!
I've taken more than my fair share of keys in my life.
So taking one more key like yours is gonna be a snap.
Coin, coin, coin, swish!
Wow! I can't believe you just went "coin, coin"!
And then flew away like "swish!"
Hakase! I have a question for you!
Lemme catch my breath.
I was laughing so hard I forgot how to breathe.
Listen, I can't help but notice that I'm
making some pretty strange reactions today.
You didn't, you know, do something to me,
did you now?
Well, actually, I gave you a funny bone feature yesterday!
Shibibi! Shibibi!
Why would you give me such a
bizarre and obnoxious feature?
What is even the point of it anyway?
I thought it would be funny.
Thump!
Goal!
Dodododo!
Mwah!
Bang!
This is it.
This is how I'm gonna die and it's gonna be awful.
See how much fun we're having?
I'm not having any fun!
All right then.
Forget about the key for a sec and
please just remove this funny bone feature.
That'll be a hundred yen.
Boom!
This takes every last ounce of my strength.
I'm oil.
People say I'm slippery, but I can't really blame them!
That's just who I am.
My boss pours me all the time, but
you're not the boss of me, so hands off!
The next episode of My Ordinary Life is Episode 16.
Look forward to it!