Nano Shinonome.
I've used every single trapping trick I have up my sleeve.
Since you still remain out of my reach,
your system has to be far more advanced
than I initially thought,
and I must know what makes you tick!
For science!
Unfortunately, my various attempts at capturing
you have garnered some unwanted attention at school.
I must tread carefully.
Hm?
Could that be...?
Wait!
Come back!
Don't you walk away from me!
Me-Meow!
Thanks for the food!
Wait for your father to get here first!
Aww!
Hey, Sis, have you seen the remote?
I think I saw it next to the kettle.
Meow?
Hm?
That's the wrong cat.
Who's out here snooping around at this hour?
The heck are you doing?
Is that a thief?
Not good!
Hey, lady! What's the matter with you?
Hm?
Huh. It's Nano.
Thank you very much for the help.
Those books look heavy.
Not at all.
But I appreciate the assistance.
Mm. It was the least I could do.
Mio! Hey! Guess what I just saw!
Can you tell me later? I'm busy.
It can't wait until later!
I have to tell you about it right now!
'Kay, go.
I just caught Nano and Koujirou
walking together out in the hallway!
And?
Huh?
That's weird.
I thought she would totally freak out over this.
So?
Uhh.
Hmm.
So!
They, uh, were being all polite to each other!
Hmm.
Doesn't seem like anything out of the ordinary to me.
Huh?
People talk to other people.
That stuff happens all the time.
So, yeah. Is that it?
Um, guess so.
That's all I got.
All right, well, I've gotta finish
this report before the next class.
So, you know.
I'd appreciate it if you'd stop distracting me.
'Kay, sure. Sorry.
Well, dang. That was a buzzkill.
So?
Huh?
And then?
What happened? After?
After what?
After you saw those two being
all buddy-buddy with each other.
Well?
You were so chatty just a second ago.
Well, um, he, uh...
Koujirou told Nano that he thought her
big stack of books looked really heavy.
And then?
And... then that's it.
Oh, my gosh, Yuuko!
You are so silly, you know that?
I always knew you were a total goofball, but all
of your crazy talk really cracked me up this time!
I can't believe you made such a big deal out of this!
You can be such a little dummy-dumb!
It's kinda crazy how clueless you can be!
It's fine 'cause you're dumb!
Ya idiot!
I guess I forgot to mention that after they talked,
Koujirou and Nano started making out.
What? No way.
You're kidding. How could that even happen?
Well, it started off with a little
bit of smooching here and there,
then they went to the cafeteria for a snack,
if you know what I mean.
Turns out it was an actual snack,
'cause they bought some bread,
but one thing led to another...
...snd suddenly, Koujirou...
Koujirou what?
He took his clothes off outta nowhere!
He took off his clothes?
And then he mentioned that wanted to
get his hands on something "delicious,"
so Koujirou decided to make his move.
What move?
In the courtyard.
The courtyard?
I totally forgot that I gotta do
that report thing before class, too!
Aw, crap!
We have to come up with our own
subject for this stupid assignment?
But what happened?
In the courtyard...
What did they do?
Ah? You decided to get the yakisoba bread again, I see.
So what? It's my favorite!
You sure do love that bread, don't you?
Looks like you're the Yakisoba Princess.
Well, uh...
What kind of bread did you buy then?
Me?
I bought a sweet roll.
Then... does that make him...?
Hm? What's wrong?
It's none of your business, so there! Hmph!
Does that mean... I should call him...
...the Sweet Roll Prince?
How delicious!
Then... does that make him...?
Hm? What's wrong?
It's none of your business, so there! Hmph.
So then... does that mean...
...I should call him... the Silky-Skinned Beauty?
Let's eat in the courtyard!
What a splendid idea.
And then I heard the teacher ate a
whale that was caught in the wild!
Ha! That's preposterous!
I'm telling the truth!
But, if that's the case, it means they went outside of
the established 200 nautical mile exclusive fishing zone.
Oh, that's no problem at all, because
the teacher is actually an Inuit!
Nano.
Hmm?
There's a crumb on your cheek.
Let me get that for you.
It was like a gentle moment
floating on the soft spring breeze.
Our moment.
in the courtyard.
Our rendezvous.
Rendezvous!
How am I supposed to focus like this?
I can't stop thinking about those two!
I have to know!
Yuuko!
I was just about to think of a topic!
Tell me what happened between those two in the courtyard!
Will you stop yelling at me?
Let's see.
They were, uh...
You're useless!
Fine then! I'll have to find out myself!
I'll go to the Courtyard of Eden!
Thank you again for your help.
It was my pleasure.
Farewell.
Huh? Mio, are you okay?
Why are you on the floor?
Nano.
Yes?
I heard that you were eating yakisoba
bread with Koujirou out in the courtyard.
And who is Koujirou?
Uh... oh, you mean that guy?
All he did was help me pick up
one of the books I dropped earlier.
And that's it?
Yup. That's all that happened.
But... what happened to the yakisoba bread?
Huh? What are you talking about?
Helvetica Standard.
Hey!
Come on, you can trust me!
Just tell me who you like, Yumi!
Aww.
I dunno if I should.
I won't tell anybody,
but if I do, I'll give ya a million yen! 'Kay?
All right.
But you better not tell anyone, you promise?
Yeah, totes!
It's Takashi.
Hey, everyone, listen up!
Yumi just told me that she likes Takashi!
Fascinating.
Ha!
Head!
Thank you for all your help today.
Take this.
Huh?
That stupid prodigy!
It's so rare for you stop by the dojo nowadays.
With the competition coming up,
it's good to get some extra lessons
with our instructor outside of school,
so I can be ready.
And having Yoshino there also
helps out with my training a lot, too.
You're lucky, because she usually never shows up.
What? She doesn't?
She told me she actually starts
to get worse the harder she trains.
Like some kendo freak of nature.
So, if you don't learn from her, who
do you normally get your lessons from?
The instructor.
And Sasahara has also been
coming to the dojo a lot lately.
Hmm.
Sasahara?!
Since when does he go to the dojo?
Since always?
He was going there throughout all of
middle school, so it's really nothing new.
Yeah, but, well, I... I guess that's true.
I don't get why you're making such a big deal.
Aren't you in the same kendo club?
The one at school!
No, we are not!
He's been in the drama club ever since his first year.
Hmm?
Wha?!
He's part of the drama club?
Why isn't he in the kendo club?
How the heck am I supposed to know?
If you take a weird guy like him
out of something cool like kendo,
all you're left with is a weird dude!
You don't know Sasahara like I do,
'cause you've only ever seen him at the dojo.
What do you mean?
I mean that his performances in
the drama club are a bit out there,
but they're honestly pretty unique and interesting.
Don't be silly. This is grape juice.
I guess I can imagine that.
So, you get it?
What I don't get is why you haven't
just invited him to the kendo club yet.
It's such a waste!
What?
Why do I have to be the one to invite him to the club?
I don't think about him. He can do whatever he wants.
But I bet you guys could totally make
it to nationals together with his help!
Don't hold your breath.
He ran off and joined that stupid
little drama club of his own accord.
Who cares? I don't! That idiot!
But if you insist...
There's no need to twist my arm.
Maybe I can invite him for your sake.
Oh, wow.
I can read her like a book.
So?
Huh?
When does Sasahara come to the dojo?
Uh...
Well, he stops by every three days or so, so I get
the feeling that he'll probably be there tomorrow.
Mm...
'Kay, whatever. It's not like I care.
Hey, Sis.
What?
You should just confess your feelings to him already!
I don't wanna hear it from someone younger than me!
I'm going home!
Sis. You're so transparent.
It's freezing!
Icy hand attack!
See ya!
Fascinating.
Yuck.
Mm!
Ahh, so yummy!
Thank you for all of the food!
Hakase!
You need finish those green
onions you flicked to the side!
I think it's still a bit too early
for me to eat green onions right now.
What is that supposed to mean?
Regardless,
you should finish every bit of food that's on your plate.
But the green stuff is always bitter,
and gross, and weird, and whatever.
If you don't finish your food,
then you don't get snacks tomorrow.
Just look at Sakamoto and follow his example.
He eats his food no matter what...
Sorry. I'm just not feeling it.
Oh, no! What happened?
Aw, come here, kitty! Are you doing all right?
I'm fine. It's just a little cold.
I'll sleep it off...
You'll have a hard time recovering if you don't eat.
Can you at least give it a try?
I think I'll pass.
Would it help if I got you some milk?
Don't think so.
Then I'm at a loss.
Do you feel like eating anything at all?
Not really.
I don't even wanna think about it.
Oh, no.
Here, Sakamoto, you can have my green onions.
Ya tryin' to kill me?!
Ooh.
Are you sure there's nothing I can get for you?
Yeah.
Then I'll just leave this milk right
here in case you change your mind.
If you need anything at all, let me know, okay?
Sure.
I think I'm coming down with a
cough, so can you get me some chocolate?
Please and thank you.
Only if you eat your green onions.
Why does Sakamoto get offered stuff for free but I don't?
Because Sakamoto's sick and needs the help.
Well, I'm coughing over here, so I can be sick, too!
Sick people usually aren't this energetic.
I just really want chocolate and it's pumping me up!
I can be sick and excited at the same time!
If you're actually sick,
then you have to take some medicine.
So, do you wanna take medicine?
Forget it!
Wait, Hakase!
Did you put yourself in timeout?
Leave me alone!
You hate me, so that's why you're being
mean and making me eat those yucky green onions!
And you like Sakamoto more because
you're not making him eat any onions at all!
Wait, I don't think you understand.
Cats can't eat onions. It's toxic for them.
Well, how was I supposed to know that?!
You're so silly.
If I'm being honest, I actually like you the most.
Is that true?
You betcha!
So can I have chocolate now since you like me most?
Lemme think.
I'll let you have it if you eat your onions.
What? No fair!
You're being the worst most-liker of me ever right now!
Then maybe I'll just go like Sakamoto the most.
Can you make up your mind already?
Okay, I choose both of you!
That doesn't count, Sakamoto!
Which floor would you like?
The seventh floor, please, if you wouldn't mind.
The thing is,
I don't remember feeling embarrassed this year.
Now then.
Let's talk about your hopes and dreams for the future.
Hmm.
A manga artist.
Um, that's right.
Your drawings have always been
excellent, so this is great!
Huh? Well...
I believe in your skills.
So, feel free to chase your dreams.
I wish you the best of luck!
Hmm?
Let's see, Yuuko wanted the melon juice,
but what do I wanna drink?
Well, money is pretty tight this month,
so I probably shouldn't get anything fancy.
Just stick with the usual banana juice.
Oh! Wait! Don't roll away!
Sorry about that...
Wait. No. Yes? Yes! No!
It's him!
Koujirou's right in front of me!
I hope I didn't startle you.
You're practically a deer in headlights right now.
No! You're fine and I'm fine and sorry!
Mm.
Come on!
Talk about something.
Anything at all!
So, uh...
The weather sure is nice today, isn't it?
Wait! No it isn't, you idiot!
See? The sky's all gray and gloomy!
That was rich.
Yeah.
By the way, miss, might this coin belong to you?
Uh, yes!
Is that right?
Well, this is certainly a surprise.
Huh? 'Kay, sure.
Perhaps I was fated to come across you and this coin.
Huh?
This just so happens to be the only day
I've forgotten to bring my wallet with me to school.
And right as my throat was becoming parched,
I was conveniently walking near a vending machine.
And lo, I picked up this coin.
The heavens... are shining down on me.
In a way,
the drink I'm to receive is like ambrosia,
passed down to me directly from on high.
Um...
This vending machine...
Huh! Looks like it can be quite the prankster!
Oh! Yeah!
To think.
A simple dispenser of drinks managed to get the best me.
Must be a bold contraption to be
able to pull off such an admirable feat.
I like it!
You deserve my coin, you dastardly device!
Uh, Koujirou?
Shh.
I don't really know why, but...
...I feel like I've gotten a little closer to him.
Mio! Where's my juice?
I wonder if she was trying to tell me something.
Yoshino is so strong and skilled,
she's practically unstoppable.
The Knight.
What does it mean?
What do I do with it?
Confess your feelings already!
Hey, Sis, the bath is free now.
Uh...
I wonder.
Is Koujirou looking at the moon right now, too?
Sasahara!
You're not half bad, y'know!
You should come back and train with me sometime!
Mm.
Cool!
I might even teach you my secret move next time!
Sis!
Look, what's that over there?
Hm?
Sisters!
Don't barge into my room and scare me like that!
I wasn't interrupting a special moment, was I?
No, of course not!
Don't worry about it!
Are you blushing?
No! I'm not!
Just leave me alone!
I'm a vending machine, and here's my MO.
When you're low on cash and need a snack,
we'll eat your change and won't give it back!
Respect my law!
The next episode of My Ordinary Life is Episode 25.
Look forward to it!