All right! Everyone ready to play?
Rock!
Paper!
Scissors!
Aw, man!
Aw, yeah!
Looks like I'm going first.
♪ De-Li-cious pine-ap-ple! ♪
Rock! Paper!
Scissors!
Sweet! Here I come!
Hey, hold up! Rules say only one step at a time!
Oh, I'm well aware.
G-Li-co
Cor-por-ation.
Cheater!
What? But how?
You can't add stuff on at the end!
Why? I'm just using the company's full name.
Hey! That's fair, isn't it Mai?
Fifty-fifty.
Okay, fine. I'll let it slide.
But next time, I'm allowed to bend the rules to
work in my favor so we can even things out a little.
Now, rock, paper, scissors.
Look at that! Mai gets to go next!
Chi-yo-ta.
Ni-ke-Ra-ha-to-ho- Ra-su-Te-no-ha-Te...
...ki-Ra-to-Na-ri-ha-shi-Te-to.
Incantation of Revival.
It stopped working.
Aww, mom!
I thought I told you to wake me up at seven!
Where were you?!
Uh.
Seriously? Kick volleyball?
Just perfect!
I am gonna be so late!
Of all days, that alarm clock just had to
choose the most inconvenient time to crap out!
Even in death, I guess it found a way to
alarm me, but that's not the way it's supposed to!
Ugh, I hate irony!
All right, if I book it at my top speed,
I might be able to make it.
Wait. Hang on.
Rewind.
There was something beary suspicious!
Please tell me it's gone.
Nope! Here it comes!
Whoa, what the what?!
Who is this pro sprinter?!
And what are they doing chasing little ol' me?
There it goes!
Bring it.
Um. Excuse me.
Did you happen to drop this wooden fish?
Uh!
Or perhaps, it was this golden one?
I'm so dead.
I have no choice.
There's only one way.
Please take this and go.
Sometimes, I can be a bear.
And other times, I can be...
...hard to bear.
However! My true identity is...!
Oh! That was priceless!
Tada!
It was actually your older sister this entire time!
Bet you didn't see that coming,
since I used your uniform as a disguise.
Man! That was a bla...
Hm... A rather commendable
corkscrew punch on this fine morning.
Indeed! It was quite beautiful to behold!
Hey, give me some credit.
Disabling your alarm clock to set this up wasn't easy.
So it's all your fault!
All right, just chill out. I'll make it up to you.
I know, we can go get some ramen, on me. 'Kay?
That's my money in the first place!
Chi... yo... ta...
Ni-ke-ra-ha-to
ho-ra-su-te-no-ha-te-ki
ra-to-na-ri-ha-shi-te-to.
A shark. Wow!
I'm home!
Oh! What are you up to, Hakase?
Nano! Check it out!
That cloud's a shark!
Oooo! Let me sneak a peek.
Would you look at that!
Isn't it awesome?
It really is.
That's right! Almost forgot. Look what I bought for you!
Milk.
Is it 4.5%? That's the best!
Yup, it's the creamier kind.
But why this specific type?
And what made you want it so suddenly today?
Heh! Oh, you'll see.
It goes great with my swiss roll!
Wait!
Why would you install such a strange additional feature?
I needed you to hold my cake.
That doesn't make any sense!
Nano! Please pass me the milk!
This isn't the time for that!
I think I have the right to be informed
when a whole cake is being stored inside my arm!
Ah! So yummy and cold!
Please stop ignoring the issue.
Imagine if someone outside saw my arm open.
Rolly, rolly, roll! Rolly, rolly, rolly!
Excuse me.
What's up?
I, uh. Could I have some cake too, please?
Yeah, sure.
Gimme one second.
Here ya go!
I really appreciate it.
Uh. You kind of forgot the cake part.
Huh?
I know! I have an extra sweet bun you can eat!
Help yourself!
It went back in!
Oops! That's my bad!
I accidently pushed the button.
Ahh! Why do you keep installing
so many bizarre functions in me?
Have you ever even considered how people would
react if they saw my head pop open in public?
What would happen?
Well, uh...
Didja hear their new album?
Yeah, it was great!
'Kay! I'll add a feature that lets you play music!
I think you missed the point!
I'd like you to stop adding functionalities for no reason!
You're not listening to me at all, are you?
Jeez...
Uh?
What is it?
A sweet bun.
No you don't!
Not after you already had an
entire swiss roll to yourself.
What?!
Something wrong, what'd I do?
'Kay, Fine!
I'll just have my other bigger, better, rolly-rolly cake!
What?! Really?!
Not again! Where is it going to come out from this time?
My stomach? Or my leg? Or...
For real?
Wait, why didn't you just put all of the
food in the refrigerator from the beginning?
Don't wanna!
Wha...?!
♪ First comes a rock, what's it gonna be? ♪
♪ Rock-paper-scissors and a one, two, three! ♪
I'm pooped.
Oh, Mio!
What's up? Your face looks weird.
Can I see your homework?
Don't tell me that you forgot to do yours again.
Well... I'm not exactly proud of it.
Girl, you know you're never
gonna learn if you keep doing this.
Oh, yeah, I get that.
Come on. Just this one time?
I promise I'll never do it again. Please?
Yuuko.
That's what you say every time this happens.
I swear on my life!
Yeah, and you say that every time, too.
Oh. Do I?
Fine. Twist my arm, why don'tcha.
This is for real the last one.
Like, for real, real.
I hear ya loud n' clear!
You're totally saving my butt with this, Mio!
Hey, Yuuko!
You have to come over here and see this.
All right, I'll bring this back as soon as I'm done.
Coming! Lemme see what you got!
Hang on.
I get the feeling I'm forgetting something important.
After finishing my homework last night...
I did a thing...
I won't...
I drew something.
...let you.
And that thing I drew...
I forgot to erase it!
I won't let you do this.
It's still in there!
Hey! Got a little problem here!
Yeah, I getcha!
I know!
Yuuko!
Hey, I just remembered that I
totally forgot to do my homework, too!
So, you don't need my notebook after all!
So, yeah, I'll be taking this thing back now.
Sorry 'bout it!
Yuuko?
Come on, you don't need it anymore...
I know you're just trying to pull a fast
one on me, but I'm not gonna fall for it!
I'll have it back in no time, I promise!
'Kay?
All right, now where were we?
This is bad.
Really, really bad.
If anyone sees that drawing, my
reputation is gonna go down the drain!
Why does my fate have to be in the hands of Yuuko
of all people?! If she starts spreading rumors...
It'll be catastrophic!
Yuuko!
So, turns out I gave you the wrong notebook.
This one here's for math.
Huh? But wait, look.
This says "math" right here on the front.
Never mind! I need it back, 'cause uh...
I have a bad stomach ache!
Uh-huh.
Gah!
I'll be done in a jiffy, so hold your horses, would ya?
It's all over. She's gonna see it, and then...
That's it. My short-lived high school life is done for!
Listen!
I'll buy it off you for a thousand yen!
Why are you running away?!
Come back!
Fine then! You want the truth?!
I'll tell you!
It's gonna explode!
There's no way.
She's too fast for me to catch up to her.
I'll miss you, life.
It was good while it lasted.
Thank you, existence, for everything.
We had a lot of fun, didn't we?
Sure, it got a little weird sometimes, but overall,
I was pretty happy with how things were.
But this is the end! My life is truly over now!
And my banquet of boys...
I bid you adieu, as well.
Goodbye.
Wait! There's no way I'll let that happen!
The fire in my heart... must become an inferno!
In the end...
...I failed.
Wait, Yuuko!
Stop running!
You're in the hall!
Hey. Are you okay...
Uh!
Here.
Pass your notebooks to the person in front of you.
And if you forgot your homework, please speak up now.
It was almost really bad there for a second.
But I guess all's well that ends well.
Now I can go back to living my ordinary... life.
Ahh!
Huh?
I never erased it!
Yo.
What seems to be the problem?
Teacher! I, uh...
Forgot my homework!
There we go.
Hakase, would you mind tidying up the
room and putting your stuff away, please?
Sorry, but I just don't think
I'm ready to do something like that.
I'm gonna go play now.
Uh...
But then, I ended up telling him everything anyway!
Wow, are you serious? Come on, dude!
Um, excuse me!
Annaka! Could I have a moment?
Yes?
Well, you see. This is just a minor thing, but...
I think your hair ribbon might be too big. Don't you?
But look! Bunny ears!
Sweet buns are tasty.
You said it.
Welcome, miss!
Sasahara. You do realize that you're a
member of the cultural festival committee, right?
Can you at least try to be a bit more serious about this?
Oh, I'm being quite serious.
As the president of the drama club,
I'm always doing my part around here.
Or did you perhaps not notice that, Miss Tachibana?
Don't patronize me!
It's sweet.
Would you listen?!
We're supposed to decide on the
programming for the culture festival.
Your drama club has nothing to do with it!
Seems like they changed the brands.
Why on earth did I have to be
paired up with you of all people?
It tastes quite nice.
Here I am, wasting my time when the
kendo tournament is coming up. Ah, man.
I never should have volunteered to be
a committee member in the first place.
Heh.
What are you doing?! We need to come up with an idea!
But you're too busy reading manga over here.
Sorry, but this volume was just released.
Don't you have at least one good thought?
Was my Wine Tasting Tournament idea not suitable for you?
Of course it wasn't!
I already turned it down!
Think of something!
Hey, Sasahara.
So, what's your excuse for slacking this time?!
Well. I'm fresh out of ideas, for starters.
Huh. I'm not getting a signal here.
What?! And where do you think you're going?
I'm taking a visit to the restroom.
This freakin' guy.
Huh. It seems like she was in no mood today.
I thought my Wine Tasting Tournament was
a stellar idea, but she thought otherwise.
However, she has yet to suggest a single idea of her own.
Honestly, I'd fear for my life if I mentioned that to her.
There's only one way out, I must be the
one to present an idea that she agrees with.
But that means...
I need to bring myself down to a commoner's level.
I suppose I have no other options at this point.
It's not like you're special to
me or anything like that, okay?
The purity of Asia.
I am a sweet bun.
Since I'm not very popular in the Kansai region,
people aren't exactly sure what to call me sometimes.
But now you know!
The next episode of My Ordinary Life is Episode 03.
Look forward to it!