What's up, Yuuko?
I've got zero motivation.
You serious right now?
But we like, just started a new semester.
Think of the possibilities.
I'm sure you'll find something that gets
you motivated if you get the ball rolling.
I can barely roll out of bed, let alone roll a ball.
How am I supposed to find the
motivation to be motivated, huh?
A motive for motivation. Hm...
How 'bout you just do it?!
'Kay, sure!
It must be nice to be a complete idiot.
Hakase! It's about time to get out of bed!
There we go.
Morning.
Whatcha got there?
It's a fish that I'm grilling
up for this morning's breakfast.
Fish? But I want a rice omelet!
But you had that for breakfast yesterday.
Besides, fish are packed with
essential vitamins and minerals.
If you wanna grow up to be big and
strong, you need to have a balanced diet.
Uh?
Um. Excuse me, do you mind returning our breakfast?
Uh. No, this isn't what it looks like!
It's definitely not a robotic component or anything!
You see... It's a...
He's gone!
Come back you crazy cat!
Okay, bye...
Come to think of it,
what if the cat needs that food more than we do?
Ahh! Look out!
Hi, good to see ya, Mio! Selamat pagi !
Oh, hi, Yuuko. It's nice to see you too.
You think it's okay if I don't have
my student ID? 'Cause I forgot it today.
Wait, did she miss that I greeted her in Malay?
I hope some upperclassman doesn't notice and call me out.
If one does, you can just say you're an upperclassman
too, and they'll have no idea without your ID.
That won't solve anything. I guarantee you.
That sounded like thunder, but the sky's so clear.
It might start pouring any second!
It'd suck if we got rained on outta nowhere!
It's raining wooden dolls.
Whoa! Are you all right?
How does that fall from the sky?
Yeah, that's super weird. I
wonder where it even came from.
I'm just as confused as you are.
But don't worry, I bet something as crazy as
this only happens once in a girl's lifetime.
You know. It's like a freak accident. Right?
Yeah, totally.
That must mean I'm lucky.
I'm not lucky at all.
You doin' okay down there?
It happened again with a red cow this time.
What does it mean?
Y'know, maybe it's not about luck at all.
Sometimes, bad things happen, but it could be worse.
At least I wasn't hit by something
that's disgusting like raw meat.
So, as long as that doesn't
happen, it's really not that ba..
It's raw salmon!
Good morning!
Oh, heyo!
Morning!
Good morning to you.
Oh, hey. Good morning, Mai.
Selamat pagi !
Good morning.
That looks interesting, whatcha got there?
This is a real estate magazine.
Wha--? Are you lookin' to buy a house?
Undecided.
My awesome, unique greeting gets ignored yet again.
Oh, well. I guess I have no choice but
to put this short-lived phrase to rest.
Yuuko.
Huh?
Selamat malam.
Silly Mai! It's "selamat pagi" ! Ha!
What language are they speaking?
It's, uh, time for homeroom. Take your seats.
Okay, when I arrived at school today,
I found this inside my shoe locker.
Now, did one of you kids put it in there?
Um, well, uh. If you did do it, that's okay.
I would just appreciate if you'd own up to it.
Who do you think could've pulled that kind of prank?
It's pretty bonkers, huh?
How am I supposed to know?
I bet you it was a student that has
like, a big crush on her or something.
But who would give their crush a Buddha statue?
Although, I can definitely understand the feeling
of wanting to give the person you like a gift,
so I can't really blame 'em.
Oh, that's right. It's because you have a
crush on that upperclassman Koujirou Sasahara.
Ah! Don't say it out loud!
Where am I? How did I get here?
Huh?
I have to get home.
Hakase is probably worried sick.
Plus, I left the grill on, and that's a hazard.
Oh, no. I can't get down!
Wait. My chopsticks are gone.
And I'm missing a slipper!
What do I do?
My hand's gone, too!
Ohh! Now it'll be obvious that I'm a robot!
Ready?
Thanks for the meal.
Hm? Hurry.
You gotta finish eating your
food before fifth period starts.
Wait, all you've got left is one sausage.
This is all part of my plan to save the
very best of my lunch for the grand finale.
That way, I'm for sure gonna
walk away from my meal satisfied.
Hmm...
And now, without further ado,
it's gonna go down the hatch!
Oh!
It slipped through!
I got it!
It's done for!
Over my dead body!
One... two...
three... four...
five!
It's okay!
Uh! It's totally not!
Ha, ha! Aw, chill out Mio!
Haven't you ever heard of the five-second rule?
Haven't you heard of E. coli?! That is 100% gross!
Uh!
Tasty!
She... is such... a moron...
♪ First comes a rock, what's it gonna be? ♪
♪ Rock-paper-scissors and a one, two, three! ♪
Aw...
Okay!
Good morning, students.
I hope you're having a wonderful day today.
Now that spring has sprung, it's
time to welcome a new school year.
But despite the change of seasons, the cold will stay.
Though I'm sure the cold will come to
a head for me before it does for you.
So please take care that you don't catch a cold.
After all,
it is my duty as principal to watch over you students.
But if you neglect to take my advice to
heart, and you do catch a cold, well...
I'd say you might have forgotten to
respect your principal's principles.
Can I ask you something, Mio?
Make it quick. We'll get in
trouble if they catch us talking.
Do you think the principal knows that none
of his jokes are funny to anyone but himself?
It's pretty obvious, right?
You'd think he would take the
hint when no one laughs, like ever,
but it seems like he's just in his
own little world most of the time.
Hm. I never really thought about it.
But wait!
What if he does know he's not funny,
and he's just trying to teach the younger,
lazier generation the importance of persistence?
Possibly.
If that's the case, then the principal
might actually be some manipulative mastermind!
Mai?
What's her deal?
Don't tell me she's laughing at those terrible jokes!
Huh?!
I've never seen Mai crack up this much before!
She's totally busting her gut!
All right! Here's my chance!
Hey, Mai!
I can't do it! I want to tell my own lame
joke, but it'll be too embarrassing for me!
Yuuko?
Huh?
Sorry. Never mind. It's nothing.
I think... I won't say anything.
I'll just leave it where it is.
Next on the docket, we have a necessary
message from the student counselor, Ms. Sakurai.
You can step up to the microphone whenever you're ready.
Umm, I think it's your turn.
It is?!
Excuse me!
I'm Ms. Sakurai, your student counselor.
But umm. I-I guess you knew that already.
Oh man. It's so nerve-wracking
to be in front of such a big crowd.
No, I've got to pull it together!
It's my job to be a model
teacher for my students, and myself!
I'm going to go ahead and say what needs to be said!
All right! I've noticed that there have
been some goats on the school grounds recently.
Please try your best to not bring any
goats to school with you if you can help it.
Goats, you say?
And what is so bad about goats?
Huh?
I've read the school policies.
Nowhere does it say that we can't bring a goat to class!
Um, well. That's uh...
Yo, Mio. Was that Koujirou screaming about goats?
What? Goats, where?
Mm... Then.
I guess goats are perfectly fine!
Hmph.
Like hell your goats are fine!
You don't get to make that call!
Even if it's not in the school's rules, it's still weird!
Duly noted. But consider this, Misato.
Why should someone like me be forced
to hobble to school with my own two legs?
I am the eldest son of the Sasahara household, you know.
I don't give a damn about your Sasahara household!
You guys are a buncha normal farmers!
Regardless, that does not change the
fact that I am the eldest son of the family.
For real?
Koujirou comes from a family of ordinary farmers?
And here I thought he was the greatest of all time.
That means the white goat I saw at the
bike rack must have belonged to Koujirou.
I can just imagine him riding majestically
atop that beautiful steed and whisking me away.
A happy new year to me!
I do.
Whoa!
Uh!
Uh. Also, make sure you don't use your cellphones
while riding your bikes. It's extremely dangerous!
And now finally...
I discovered this Buddha statue that
someone put in my shoe locker this morning.
I just wanted to point out that
pranks like these are unacceptable!
Excuse us! Coming through!
A Buddha statue...
Ah! Gosh, Mai! Don't stop like that without warning!
There it is again. So this is what déjà vu feels like.
Uh. Who put this inside my locker?
I promise I won't be angry if you own up to it.
We can stand here all day until
someone raises their hand and confesses.
Who actually did it?
Just say it was you.
Uhh...
Uh?
Uh. Well, I heard it was your birthday through
the grapevine, so I wanted to get you something.
Ah, I guess I know now that a Buddha
statue doesn't exactly make a great gift.
So. It seems as though one thought
it would be good to give a present.
But a Buddha statue is not so pleasant.
Sorry.
That concludes today's assembly.
Thank you for your words, and
we'll all miss you dearly, Principal.
Vice Principal!
I dunno about you, but staring at this fire
alarm button makes me wanna push it real bad.
Oh yeah, I get that.
Why don't you just push it?
I did one time and absolutely nothing happened.
Oh! Really?
A fire?
Seriously?
What do we do? Book it?
Let's all scramble out of here as fast as we can!
What do you think you're doing?
Quit pushing me!
You shoved me first, man!
Are you kidding me?
You're really starting to tick me off!
Cut it out!
Someone could die if you start a fight now!
Let's just get out of here.
You can duke it out later!
Helvetica Standard.
Excuse me.
Hey.
Sorry, but what does "being insensitive" mean?
Excuse me!
Just what does "insensitive" mean?
Do you have a moment?
Can you explain what insensitive means?
Somebody help me!
Hey!
Oh! Hi, Captain!
Can you tell me what's insensitive?
Simple. You are.
Attention. Could Koujirou Sasahara of Class 2-P
please report to Tomioka in the faculty room immediately.
We understand that it's not against the school rules.
But really, a goat? Just, why?
I'll ask nicely.
Could you please stop riding a goat to school everyday?
Why don't you ride a bike?
Mister...
Tomioka.
Don't forget the mister.
All right, Mister, I'd actually prefer it if you'd
call him "Koujirou Sasahara," and not simply "goat."
Think I'm gonna stick with "goat."
My name is Nano Shinonome.
I'm just your average robot,
and I live at home with my creator, Hakase.
Hakase spends every single day inside the
house doing all sorts of really important research.
And I spend those days by helping
her out in any way that I can.
Hakase! I brought you that warm milk you asked for...
I don't have any special features,
but apparently I'm a robot that can feel pain.
Nano? What's the matter?
Hakase! I stubbed my toe! The little one!
No!
But pinky is the littlest piggy of them all!
There, I fixed it. You should feel better now.
I don't have any special features,
but apparently my pinky toe comes off?
Could you tell me what the key on my back's for?
Oh? Have I never wound it up for you?
No, you haven't.
But it spins on its own sometimes.
Give it a little twisty-twist, and...
What's going on?
I take it back.
I have all sorts of special features.
Ya see? Pretty cool, huh?
So, that's it?
That's the only reason I have a key on my back?
That's right!
It really has no additional features other than that?
You got it!
Can you take it off?
No!
I wanna leave it on 'cause it looks cute.
But I'd really like it if you took it off.
Aww, it's so cute though.
I just wish that I could be more like a normal human.
I'd like to sit in a chair without having to twist weird.
And be able to roll over in bed when I sleep.
With this thing,
I'll never be able to go to school.
It would have been better if
you never made me a humanoid robot.
Nano...
Huh?
Uhh!
Uh. I'm just kidding. 'Kay? It's a joke.
Stop crying. Please! I'm sorry!
Fine, take it!
Huh?
Take the Akutagawa Prize!
Wait, what?!
You heard me!
Akutagawa prize! You should go get it!
This is my ordinary life.
So, uh. Where am I?
Hello there! This is Nano's big toe speaking!
Fun fact: My storage capacity is one gigabyte.
That's not a whole lot nowadays, is it?
Next time on My Ordinary Life : It's the second episode!
Look forward to it!