Man, it's so hot out.
Super-duper hot!
Ah. Can you cut it out? I feel it.
This heat has been hard on me, too.
But ya know, when you bring
it up, it makes it worse, 'kay?
So could you stop saying it's hot?
Okay, okay.
Man, it's a scorcher out here!
It's blistering. Sweltering, even!
Do ya know what I mean, man?
Feels like I'm in an oven! I'm baking out here! Broiling!
So humid!
I could punch him right now.
Nobody would know.
What's with the sun?
This gotta be a record!
Dude, seriously, it is like fire!
What a beautiful day!
The sky is blue, birds are chirping,
butterflies are fluttering.
The air, the people, and yes, even this very classroom.
Everything is great!
Because... I actually did the homework for today!
I bet Mio willl get a real kick outta this.
Huh?
Hang on. Oh, no.
No, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no.
No!
It can't be! You've gotta be kidding me!
The one time I actually did my homework?
Why?
Why did this have to happen? Why me?
Oh, well, guess I'll just have to copy it again.
Hey, Mio, question!
Hm?
Wait, our homework.
That's right. We had to... fill in a worksheet!
What's the matter with you?
Did something happen, Yuuko?
My homework. I left it at home.
There's no hope. There's nothing good in this world.
But you always forget to do your homework.
It's different this time!
I did it, but I didn't bring it!
Uh, yeah, okay I hear ya.
It's the worksheet we got yesterday, right?
You sure it isn't jammed inside your bag somewhere?
Check one more time to see.
I just turned this whole thing inside-out and got nothing.
There's no way it's...
Whoa!
My God!
Ah! What the hell is a Daifuku Fair?!
What's fair? Nothing.
Uh, don't worry about it.
Hey, who knows?
Maybe there's an extra that was left on the front desk.
Are you for real? It's a miracle!
Dammit!
Dammit, dammit! Damn all of it!
Are you going back home? But there's no time!
You're right. But I have to... try!
Uh.
Where are you off to in such a hurry?
Go and take your seats.
Twisty, twisty, twisty, twisty,
twisty, twisty, spinning, and spinning...
Slow and steady wins the race.
Out in the hall again.
Why is it that I can never get my homework in?
Am I cursed?
I always end up failing. Even when I actually finish it.
School is a cruel mistress.
Hey, Sakamoto.
Hm?
Look at my business card.
Uh? What is this about? What do I say?
What's happening?
What am I supposed to do with this?
Excuse me!
What seems to be the problem, Miss Tachibana?
Uh, nothing!
The vending machine got some new drinks,
and I was just deciding on which one I wanted.
Oh. Is that so?
Well, then, I recommend...
I don't need you to tell me what to get!
...you stay away from this option,
but the one next to it is actually quite refreshing.
Enjoy your drink.
It's not like I bought this
drink because you pointed at it!
I heard the neighborhood had some pop-up
stalls, so I decided to check them out.
I am so excited that this game is here.
A carnival shooting gallery!
I've never seen one in real life!
But all I have on me is a 500 yen coin.
I hope it'll be enough.
Step right up! One round is 500 yen!
Perfect!
Isn't that convenient?!
I wish I had enough for some yakisoba, too.
But this'll be worth it.
There's only caramels and eggplants?
Uh... Do you have any other prizes?
Whaddaya mean other prizes?
We've only got the finest quality, brand-name goods here!
He already took my money, so I might as well go for it.
Don't wanna leave empty handed.
Nice try, Miss, but you shouldn't
shoot for the grand prize right away.
Beginner's luck won't help you with that one!
Grand prize?
Why don't you aim for something smaller?
It's prob'ly more your speed!
Go ahead!
More my speed?
Whatever. Might as well go for the only other option.
So close!
Okay, that box has to be glued down.
Just a little more you and woulda had it.
Looks like you're a pretty good sharpshooter there, Miss!
Don't tell me. You're not a professional gunman, are you?
Yeah, as if!
Ah! That thing isn't budging an inch!
Oh, no. What're you making that face for?
You aren't thinking that the game is rigged, now are you?
Yeah, my stall might not be the fanciest one out there,
but an honest and genuine experience is guaranteed!
Yeah, right. There's definitely
something fishy going on here.
What is that?
Ah! Look! Right in the middle! There's a
nail! You totally nailed down that eggplant!
I'd call this whole thing a racket, wouldn't you?
Come on! Why are you giving me the silent treatment now?
Have you no shame for preying on innocent people?
I bet this entire operation is rigged!
And what happened to all that big talk
you were spewing earlier, huh?
What's the point in pretending to sleep?
I've still got one shot left
and I have a pretty good idea where to put it!
Hm?
Don't ever come back.
Like I'd want to.
Things we think are freakin' cool!
Ready, Mio? Here it comes!
Hey, nice catch!
Wow! Super bouncy balls!
Things we think are freakin' cool!
Aw! I had it!
Wow!
Slipstreams! Created by cards!
Thanks a bunch!
I haven't been to an amusement park in forever!
Right? This is so fun!
Hey, hand me my wallet, I'm gonna get a drink.
Oh. Yeah, sure. I totally forgot I was holding on to it.
Thanks for that.
But you know me; I'd probably lose it.
Ha! Yeah, I guess that's true.
Hm?
Wait, wha...?
Just hold on a second.
AH! Because I know it's inside
this zipper pocket, or maybe that one.
Hang on, I know I put it in my bag.
It should be right here, but
it's not, so maybe I might have...
I kinda, sorta, definitely lost your wallet.
I know!
Why don't we check the Lost and Found!
Maybe someone turned it in!
How much did you have in there?
Four thousand and sixteen yen.
That's specific.
Uh, we're looking for a brown bifold wallet.
And it has a snakeskin interior.
Ah, we have one just like it.
That was close. Aren't you glad we found it?
Yeah.
I dunno what I would've actually
done if I lost everything.
Attention: This is an announcement regarding a lost child.
Please listen carefully.
A young girl has been found.
She is wearing a denim shirt
that is tucked into denim shorts.
Her hat is also made of denim.
She is currently looking for her mother.
If you have any information,
please come to the lost child station immediately.
I have no clue why I thought a
stupid haunted house was a good idea!
'Kay, say cheese!
Your order is three lattes. Is
there anything else you'd like?
Oh, uh! I think...
I'd like this one, this one, and this one please.
Uh. I'm terribly sorry, miss.
But could you please provide
a specific name for the orders?
Oh, it's Sakurai.
Uh, that's not exactly what I meant.
Oh, no! I'm so sorry!
It's Izumi. The name's Izumi Sakurai.
Sorry, but I wasn't asking for your full name, either.
Sorry! I've been told it sounds
like I have two last names,
so I thought you were confused.
Well, I didn't mean your name.
All I need is the names of the items that you want.
Huh? You want names of the items?
I'm sorry, but I don't know what they are.
Oh! No. It's okay. I'm sorry for the trouble!
Yum, that food hit the spot!
I'm officially stuffed!
But I still have some room left in my dessert stomach.
Same here.
Cool! I'll do one too!
Here's mine!
I'm done, too.
Whoa! Awesome! Your stuff's great as usual.
What did you make? Done yet?
A crane?
Nano! Check it out!
Ta-da!
I put a big key on my back, too!
Isn't this cool? Now we're matching and stuff.
Yeah, I guess we are.
Since I'm like you now, I'm gonna be Nano
all day, so no calling me "Hakase," okay?
Okay, "Nano," you got it.
Meow-ch!
Already?
Uh, Hakase, did you quit, or...?
It's "Nano"! I'm being you right now!
Oh, well, I just figured since
you took the key off of your back.
I'm just giving my back a break right now.
I'm still Nano all day today.
Right. Understood.
Hey, Hakase... I mean, "Nano."
I have an idea for a game we can play!
Do ya? What'cha got?
Since you're being me, then why don't
we switch places and I can be you today?
You bet!
So then, Hakase... I mean, Nano,
would have to put her key on.
Sure!
And since I'm Hakase now,
that means I should get this key off my back.
Not a chance.
So, what do you wanna play first? Like cards or something?
Wow, these snacks are yummy!
Those are mine! And I was saving them for later!
But now... I'm Hakase... so I get all your snacks.
Ah! That doesn't make any sense!
I can Nano, but if Nano is me and gets to eat
my snacks, then I don't wanna be Nano anymore,
and Nano can just stay being Nano.
Keep it down.
Since everything is back to normal and I'm Nano again,
I guess I'm gonna go to the store
and get groceries for tonight's dinner.
Huh? I wanna go, too!
We're not gonna buy any snacks while we're out.
I'm gonna get a chocolate shark and some apple juice!
Not a chance.
Oh, come on!
No way.
Just the chocolate shark then!
It's another peaceful day
at the Shinonome Household.
The first one that says anything loses the game.
Okay.
Oh. You just said something, so that means you lost.
You didn't say when we were
starting, so technically, I'm fine.
You wanna talk about some random stuff to
get it out of our system before we start?
You have anything you wanna talk about?
Okay.
Carbonation makes drinks fizzy,
which really seems to wake you up.
I was out.
Good morning.
It looks like sleeping beauty woke up without her kiss.
Hm?
That sucks.
And why is that?
Welcome home, Master!
It's me, Cider!
I know my bubbly personality is intoxicating,
so twist off the cap, wiff the fizz,
and join my carbon-nation.
The next episode of My Ordinary Life is Episode 13!
Look forward to it!