It's more beautiful than I ever could've imagined!
Hey, what's goin' on in here?
Just the best thing ever!
Hey, be careful over there, Sakamoto!
I wouldn't want you getting
your hair on my nice new uniform.
You've been shedding a lot lately.
I see how it is. I'm just in the way now.
I'm changing, so wait out here for a few seconds.
Check me out! Isn't this the most perfect fit ever?
Uh, well, yeah!
It was made based on your
measurements, so of course it fits!
How do I look?
You look pretty good, I guess.
Ugh. You don't get it! That's not what I meant at all!
Uh. Does it make me, um... look normal?
Sure.
I suppose you look like any other school girl.
Do you really mean it?
You're the bestest kitty in the whole world, Sakamoto!
Oh, wait! Fur!
What is up with you today?
I'll tell you what's up. School!
And maybe even some new friends on the horizon!
I don't get it, but okay.
Oh, hey, Nano.
Wanna do what friends do and
grab some ice cream after school?
Uh. Yeah. That sounds wonderful.
Great! How about we go sing karaoke, too?
Huh? Really?
Well, um. Maybe.
I've never done that before!
Don't worry! I'll show you how! Come on, everyone's going!
Oh. In that case, okay.
Wouldn't that be amazing?
Hi, Nano. Morning.
Oh, Hakase! Good morning!
Look at how well the uniform fits me!
So, what do you think? Do I look all right?
Um, yeah! You look cool!
Thanks, Hakase!
And I think you look cool in your pajamas!
You mean it? I'm cool?
You are super-duper cool!
But she wears that same thing all the time.
Sakamoto! Don't worry, you're cool, too!
Handkerchief, check! Student ID, check!
Textbooks, check! Notebook, check!
Pencils, check! Extra lead, check!
And mechanical pencil, check!
Okay! Everything is here!
What is it?
You're forgetting something.
Huh? Am I really?
What'll you do if you're hungry?
Grab a Snickers!
Good thinkin'!
I left some food in the kitchen for you.
There should be enough for breakfast and lunch.
And I'll take care of the laundry later today,
so make sure to gather the clothes you
want washed before I get home from school.
Okay, but what time will you be getting out of school?
Well, it ends around 3:30, I think.
But I'll need to do some
shopping for dinner on the way back,
so I should be home by 5:00, at the latest.
At 5:00?
What's up? Did I forget to tell you that?
Five o'clock is like nighttime.
I guess. But that's just how it's gotta be.
'Kay, I'll be on my wa...
Hey, uh, what's the problem?
I changed my mind!
What?
But you were completely on board with it a second ago.
I don't want you to go! You can't go!
No way! I'm gonna be late for school!
So could you please just give me back my...
Ah! My left hand!
Rolly, rolly, rolly, rolly, rolly, rolly, roll.
Listen, kid! Now really isn't the time for this.
Hakase.
How about I make it up to you by cooking
your favorite rice omelet for dinner?
No strings attached!
Okay then.
I'll pick up some shark castellas while I'm out shopping.
And I'll, uh... I'll throw in
an extra strawberry juice, too!
Rolly, rolly, rolly, rolly, rolly, rolly, roll.
Also.
What is it?
Win the Akutagawa prize.
But that's impossible!
I was starting to get worried there for a second,
but thankfully, I was able to convince her.
Today marks the first step
towards me becoming a normal person!
Oh, no! It totally slipped my mind!
What am I gonna do about this key on my back?
Things we think are freakin' cool!
Let's do this! It's time to get to work!
Awesome! A motivated upperclassman!
What should I do?
I've been thinking all morning,
but I can't come up with anything.
And there's no way I can back out now.
Now then, I'd like to introduce our new transfer student.
Miss Shinonome?
Yes!
I knew it! Everyone's freaked out by my key!
Here.
Miss Shinonome, take this and write
your name on the chalkboard, please.
Oh, no. Now they're all staring at my back!
I've gotta come up with an excuse quick!
Uh, hi. My name's Nano Shinonome!
And, um, you see.
I, uh, I was on my way to school, and then I fell?
And a key got stuck to me!
That made it worse! How do I fix this?
Uh, that story I told you, just, uh, forget about it!
I was kidding!
Oh, no! Now it's even more suspicious!
Uh, let's see. I've gotta say something. Anything!
It's not like my big toe will fly off and
turn into a USB drive if you wind up the key,
or anything weird and robotic like that!
I'm so dead!
♪ Tomorrow the weather will be nice! ♪
Come on, Sekiguchi.
Put the book down and let's play something.
Please, I even brought the Game
of Life for the two of us to play.
Man, this is so boring.
I guess we could try playing Go
for once, or maybe even soccer.
We are the Go+Soccer club.
Um, excuse me!
Hello!
Is there where I can find the Go+Soccer club?
Yeah?
Are you accepting new members right now?
Welcome to the club!
So what do I call ya, kid?
I'm Makoto Sakurai, and I'm a first year.
Well, my name's Kenzaburou Daiku, a
second year and the club president.
And this here's Sekiguchi, who's also a first year.
Come on in and have a seat!
Yeah, okay.
So, what do you wanna play?
How 'bout a round of this board game.
Well, uh, I was hoping that we could practice.
For?
Um, for Go+Soccer?
Don't be silly. That's a fake game I made up.
It's not like it's supposed to be a real sport.
See, this club is pretty much just about relaxing inside
and playing a few random games every once in a while.
Kinda like a recreational thing. Know what I mean?
Sure.
Hm?
The thing is,
I was actually in a Go+Soccer club in middle school.
Uh?
And I had absolutely no idea there would
be a Go+Soccer club in high school, too.
But then I saw those banners
hanging on front of the building.
So I had to find the club and join!
And not to brag, but I was the
MVP of my middle school club!
Uh, Miss Shinonome?
Oh. Yes?
Oh, I just... I was just curious about something.
Uh, that thing on your back.
Uh! It's.... Uh, well.
Huh? Right. Yeah, no. Uh.
Um. This is... Uh!
Well, I mean. Um!
So then, if Go+Soccer is a real sport,
how do you play?
Well, it can be kinda complicated,
so it'd be better if I show you.
Here. I'll give you a little demonstration.
First off is the lifting.
After lifting, its Go stones!
And then you go into...
...a solo suplex!
And that's the avalanche joseki !
Three Star Point!
That was incredible.
I never thought this club would
go anywhere when I started it.
But now, it's way cooler than I ever imagined!
Hey, wait up!
Where the heck do you think you're running off to?
Buddy! Come back!
Sakamoto! C'mere! C'mere! C'mere!
Hey! Are you crazy?! Cut that out!
If asked what it is, it is spinning.
That's what I told him.
Yeah, you see what I mean, bro?
Hey, let's go!
I told you we'd make it back early.
I can't believe I messed everything up on my first day.
Everyone probably thinks I'm crazy.
Oh, hey, Nano, did you bring your own lunch?
Uh, yeah, I did.
It looks really tasty.
So, do you pack one every day?
Yes, I do!
Like a normal girl.
Hm?
You can look at this.
Wow. It is pretty cool.
Thank you!
Oh, hells yeah. I'm right on time.
Uh, no. You're crazy late.
Lunch break is almost over already.
I'm sorry!
My shoes flew off while I was on my way
back, and they got stolen by a car and a dog,
so it was a real pain to get 'em back.
Huh?
That sounds fake, but also kinda interesting.
I totally wanna hear the whole story later.
But right now, I'm just glad you made it here all right.
Hang on. Where's your lunch?
Hm?
I ate it while I was on the way back.
Huh? What'd you have?
A twice-cooked pork lunch box.
Whoa! How did you even...?
Ugh. Never mind.
Anyway, did you wanna eat
lunch with the three of us, Nano?
I'd really like to hang out with
you and get to know you better.
Um, okay.
Maybe I didn't freak them out
and they think I'm normal after all.
Maybe I can even make some friends!
Oh, hey, what's with that strange key thing on your back?
Uh! Uhh...
It's definitely nothing suspicious
if that's what you're asking! So, uh...
You aren't actually like some
weird robot girl or something, are ya?
Don't be ridiculous, Yuuko.
Sorry, she can be kinda dense.
Oh, we're almost out of time.
Sorry, Nano. Let's have lunch together tomorrow.
Let's see.
There's no way they're gonna believe that!
Uh...
No, seriously.
I climbed the entire mountain
looking for her, and by the...
Hey, Yuuko, what did you get me?
Hm? I got the yakisaba .
...but she's just an urban legend.
Could you repeat that one more time, please?
Uh. Yakisaba , right?
I said yakisoba !
Oh. Well...
I guess I heard you wrong and got you a different thing.
Yeah, that's my bad.
Don't act like it's not a big deal! I
asked for noodles and you gave me a fried fish!
But can you blame me?
Those two names sound so similar.
That's not the...
Uh.
Whatever. I give up.
Just give me my rice.
Hm?
What rice?
The rice that comes with the fish!
Oh. Yeah, no, it's just the fish.
How am I supposed to eat this by itself?!
Huh? But you didn't clarify when you
asked for the yakisaba in the first place.
I asked for yakisoba !
Yaki ! Soba ! They're noodles!
'Kay. I get it now.
On the bright side,
you could post this whole story on
social media and I bet it'll be hilarious.
I don't own a computer!
Aww. Well, it's not my fault you're
missing out on a chance to score some likes.
All right, fine. I'll run out again and get you your food.
I just need money.
Why should I be the one who has to pay for your mistakes?
'Cause I don't have any money left on me.
Uh?
Okay, fine. Just hurry up and come back quick.
We hardly have any time left.
You can count on me!
That's all I have.
Wha...?
One peso is all I have!
I can't believe the only money in my
wallet is this peso I kept as a souvenir.
Huh?
What can I do with a single peso?
One peso?
I don't know!
You're the one who caused this mess in the first place!
You should be the one to pay for it!
I already spent all my money when I
bought my lunch, so I don't have any more.
And what am I supposed to do about my lunch?
Well, I guess... you could eat...
...the mackerel.
Mackerel?! Ugh!
You're just a never-ending cycle of pissing me off!
And I'm sick of letting you copy my homework every day!
Why don't you just do it by yourself for a change?!
You idiot!
I understand that you're upset,
but the fact that I'm an idiot has absolutely
nothing to do with me getting your lunch order wrong.
It has everything to do with it!
Yeah? I'd like to hear why!
Only an idiot would mishear me like that!
Hmph.
Everyone's guilty of making a
few mistakes sometimes, ya know!
But you just have to overreact!
It's not the end of the world!
I didn't eat breakfast, so I needed that
lunch to keep me from starving all day!
I wouldn't expect an idiot like you to understand!
I'm not an idiot!
You just said you were an idiot earlier!
Oh, and FYI, I'm never letting
you copy my homework ever again,
so good luck!
Yeah, that's fine! But this is a two-way street!
If I can't copy your homework,
then you can't copy mine either!
Why would I wanna copy your homework in the first place?
Your answers would be as wrong as my lunch order!
Which you never apologized for, by the way!
So get on your knees and apologize right now!
Fine, if that's what you really want,
I guess I should just bend over then!
How's that?
This good enough for you, Miss Perfect Hearing?
There's my apology! Are you happy now?! Are ya?!
What?! You call that weird pose you did a bow?
No! It wasn't a bow because I was just stretching!
And I'm never gonna bow to you! Fool!
Why can't you just admit that you messed up?
Because you pissed me off!
Also, calling me an idiot would make you a hypocrite.
Did you remember those weird doodles you drew?
'Cause I do!
Wait, the doodles were, uh...
You moron, those were just...
What were they?
Go ahead and tell me! I'm an idiot, so I
won't get it unless you spell it out for me!
Go ahead!
You moron!
You're a complete and utter moron!
Ugh! Who's the moron?!
Only a real moron would draw these weird
sketches and leave them out in the open!
Come on, I want you to taste defeat!
Eat it along with this yakisaba !
I wanted yakisoba !
Would you apologize already?
Get down on your knobby knees right now!
I apologized earlier!
Was that not good enough for you?
Apologize like you mean it,
or you're just a waste of space!
All right, fine!
I'll show you the ultimate bow to end all bows!
Behold its glory!
The one true bow!
Hmph. I see the bow, but I don't hear an apology!
What are you sorry for? Tell me!
Say that you're sorry for messing up my order!
Say it!
Say that you're an idiot that messes things up!
And you're just a useless human
being that can't get anything right!
Come on! I'm waiting! Do it already!
Are you not listening?
Apologize, you moron!
Worthless! Idiot! Moron!
I'm sick and tired of you constantly calling me a moron!
You don't even know me!
We've only been friends for like, what,
six lousy months now?
I could say the same about you!
You don't understand me or my drawings!
I do understand!
Your drawings are so good that you might
as well become a professional manga artist!
Uh! What are you talking about? Stop being stupid, stupid.
Huh?
Well, if I'm stupid, then you're stupid, too, so suck it!
You just called yourself stupid.
I did not!
But you did!
But that stupid side of you isn't all that bad.
What are you saying? You've got the good side!
Uh. Hey, you stop it now, with your positive energy.
Well, I think you're way too
talented at drawing art things!
Shut up! You run too fast!
Well, you're too smart!
Well, you're optimistic!
You're a great person!
You're a super fun person!
Amazing!
Captain! I'm sorry. We tried!
Save your tears. We always have next year.
I'll win it! I'll win for him!
Woohoo!
Those were the days.
Hey, Nano,
did you have fun on your very first day?
I sure did.
So many things happened. It was kinda like...
Oo, like what? Tell me about it!
I love having friends!
It's the greatest feeling in the whole world!
That sounds amazing!
Come on. You're both getting too excited.
Huh? One of these?
Hakase!
Please take this key off of my back!
Uh...
No way.
Huh? But why not?
It's having a negative impact on my life at school!
People are already starting to
suspect that I might really be a robot!
And that makes it harder for me to make friends.
You can to make friends. Your key is pretty.
I don't think it is.
But it's cute. And it's a key.
But why?
Just hurry up and give me my food.
It's soccer ball here.
All I do is get kicked around, day in and day out.
Kicked and crushed until I deflate and get put to rest!
I don't even have goals!
The next episode of My Ordinary Life is Episode 15.
Look forward to it!