Sorry it took a while!
I present to you the Yuuko special! Here.
Whoa! Your twice-cooked pork looks delicious!
And great timing too! I was getting pretty hangry.
I made sure to throw in a dash of my secret ingredient.
I wonder if you'll guess it.
You must've gone all-out if
you put your secret ingredient in.
Thanks for all the food!
Oh. That's the overpowering burst of miso.
It's so not subtle at all, not even a little bit.
No, yeah, that's all I'm getting.
Not much of a "secret" ingredient.
Ugh, now it's starting to taste worse the longer I chew.
You know what? This is one secret I wish I didn't know!
Wow, this isn't half bad!
Hey, Mio! Check it out!
Uh.
The heck is this?
A kappa? Why would she show me her weirdo drawing?
And does she really think this thing looks good?
But you know.
I do like the idea of drawing some
sort of mythical or fantasy-themed story.
Like this kappa and a daidarabotchi or something.
Kappa, hmm.
He'd be the bottom.
Kappa...
Kappa?
Huh?
Kappa... Kappa...
Pa... Parasite.
Heh. Might as well turn this into one
of those last-syllable drawing games.
Here you go.
Cool, thanks.
A parasite?
Is that what a parasite is supposed to look like?
Wait, does this little arrow mean what I think it means?
She's challenging me to a word-chain game with pictures!
Well, I accept your challenge!
Let's see, parasite.
Site... Tuh... Tuh...
Got it!
It's huge! What is that even supposed be?
A tengu maybe? Sure, let's go with that.
Whatever.
Tengu it is. Now, what starts with a "G-U"?
Guh... Goo...
Gah! Are you kidding me? Tengo ?
What the heck is a "tengo" anyway?!
Wait! Hold on a sec!
This has to be on purpose, right?
There's no way someone could
make such a basic spelling mistake.
Then again, it is Yuuko, so
we're kinda grading on a curve.
I don't get her at all.
It doesn't make any sense, but I just have to move on.
Starting with "G-O," huh?
Here.
Oh. Whoa, what's with the sensual-looking dude?
Wait. Goku?
But the last thing I drew on
my turn was a tengu, wasn't it?
Oh well, I guess it was an honest mistake.
It could happen to anybody, so I'll let it slide.
I'll give her crap about it later.
Let's see.
So, the next one can start with a "U." 'Kay!
Uh...
An eel? Wait, rabbit?
It's a cow? That looks udderly terrible!
Here.
Ohh! A tongue?
So that's how we're playing!
So, "shita" would end it a "T-A."
Then how 'bout Taxi.
Huh? Ah! What the hell?
You cannot be serious right now!
How hard is it to spell Taxi?!
Whatever, I'll keep playing along.
Mm-hm. Mm-hm. Mm-hm.
She really is trying to keep me on my toes!
Breakin' out the slang, huh? Okay, I see you.
Oh. Oh, crap! This ends with an "N"!
If I pass that over, I lose. Stupid rules.
Okay. Quick fix.
Thanks.
I'm so bored.
I said I'm bored, Sekiguchi.
Hey, I have an idea! Let's play a game of Issei-no-Sei!
I'm gonna go first!
Issei-no-Two!
Aw, man come on.
I've got nothing to do, so try to play along.
Take a look.
Did you really...?
Forget your homework.
Forced to stand out in the hall.
Uh... "Mogami River"
by Yuuko.
I can't believe I have to stand in the hallway
just because I forgot one little assignment.
I'm stuck in the hall. What to do to pass the time?
"Mogami River" by Yuuko.
Wha...?
Uh, wha...? What the...?
Why is there a...
Guys? Anyone? There's a deer.
What? The principal is out there with it?
The principal! He's gonna... The deer!
There's a deer!
Oh, no! Someone get help!
The principal is...
Is that... a cookie?
Somebody, please! It's the principal! He's...
Oh my god.
He's up!
He jumped!
Ahh! And he ate it!
He's getting up again!
He changed his mind!
Is it a stalemate?
It's not!
He's dead!
Ohh! Guys! There's a death!
He died! He's dying!
He's on his feet!
Hey! Anyone?
Everyone! You're not gonna...!
U-Uh. I mean... There's um...
It's uh... Out... side.
Uhh...
Uh, duh.
The hallway is perfectly normal!
In that moment, she spoke the honest
truth, from the bottom of her heart.
She wasn't protecting the principal,
nor was she too lazy to explain what had happened.
No, that's not the reason.
Perhaps, in the spirit of competition, she was respecting
the two brave combatants that fought for their very lives.
Early summer rain, pours down and flows through waters.
"Mogami River."
What's that even mean?
All right! Let's do this thing!
Mio! You can be the referee.
You don't need a referee for ten-yen soccer.
Uh-uh-uh. You don't get it!
You gotta set the mood! It's all about the atmosphere!
Now! Kick-off time!
Have it your way.
Now gimme your best shot! C'mon!
'Kay...
♪ First comes a rock, what's it gonna be? ♪
♪ Rock-paper-scissors and a one, two, three! ♪
Wha...!
Chomp!
I love him!
I trapped a cockroach.
He's under this cup. But what do I do now?
Okay. Think.
I have to go about this carefully.
I can't let this disgusting
menace desecrate our home any longer!
I need to come up with a plan
to keep him from tormenting us!
But what can I do?
The bug spray! No, that won't work!
It won't kill instantly, so the
roach might be able to run away.
And besides...
I don't want to see him flail
in the final throes of death!
I know! Maybe the dish soap!
If I spread it on the table, it
might slow the sucker down when
it's trying to escape! And then
I can go for the finishing blow!
It's jumping!
Animals put up the biggest fight when they're
cornered! So, it might leap past the soap!
It could even make a desperate charge right at me!
What if it touches me, or gets on me?!
No, what if it gets on my face?!
Or worse! What if... it jumps into my mouth?
If it does... I couldn't go on.
It'd be a one-shot kill!
This is it!
I have no other options!
Once I lift this bowl, it's
on! It's destroy or be destroyed!
Do or die!
Then again... there might be another way.
Huh? What's going on in here?
Hey! Sakamoto!
You have to help me!
There's... a roach... in... the cup!
Right here!
A what? Uh!
You want me to take care of a bug?
Mm-hm! Mm-hm!
Just leave it to me. Now, let me at 'em.
You're my hero!
Hey.
Yeah?
What do you think you're doing?
Lift the cup. I got this.
Really?
Well, I mean, if you don't lift it, I
can't do my job. So move your hand already.
Come on!
No way! Why would I release it?
I can't break the seal that's
containing this minion of evil!
It's like Pandora's box! If I
open it, I'm gonna unleash a demon!
What are you talking about?
There's no way I can help you
out if you don't show me that bug!
So, lift it yourself then!
I don't have thumbs!
Great. Now what do I do?
Sakamoto got fed up and ran off.
Hey, Nano!
You have any yummy snacks I can eat?
Perfect timing!
She's never been bothered by bugs before, so maybe...
Hakase! I trapped a gross cockroach under this cup!
And I'd really appreciate it
if you took care of him for me!
Sure thing!
You're an angel!
Oh, now don't mind me. You go and do your thing.
All righty then! I'll bonk the
little buggy with a really good bop!
Bam!
Uh. It looks like I missed.
Here I am, in actual, genuine distress,
but she's goofing off and making jokes, at my expense!
You know!
I really hate you sometimes, Hakase!
She's crying?
Oh, don't give me that! I was just
kidding! You can forget what I said!
There's no way I could ever hate you!
Not in a million years!
Come on. You know I love you!
Nano!
Oh, Silly! I can't stay mad at you!
Now! It's do or die! Let's rock!
It's getting too hot, so can I get out?
Get out? But you just got in a moment ago.
Yeah, but it's still too hot.
How about we count to ten,
and after that, you can get out.
Twenty log square root ten!
Huh?
That equals ten, so I can leave now?
Well... I meant...
One... Two... One at a time, like that!
Aww.
Man, this sucks.
I can't believe everyone left for cram school.
Mm? Well, I'm bored out of my mind, aren't you?
Oh yeah, weren't you supposed to be at cram school too?
Hm?
You skipped?!
Wow!
How's that curry? It smells nice!
Good! It's just about ready!
Man, it better be. I'm starving over here.
Tell me about it.
How's the fishing going, Mai?
I sense a big catch.
We're gonna eat well today!
All right! Looks like it's all done now!
Thanks for waiting!
Get ready for some super ultra-great delicious curry!
Gimme a little longer!
I should've put the rice on before we started the curry.
Oh well, as long as it's tasty,
it's better late than never, I guess!
You know what I mean?
Oh, if we brought some mayonnaise,
I bet that would really hit the spot.
Mayo does go great with curry, doesn't it?
Uh, yeah. Mayo.
Wouldn't you say so?
I felt sick.
No, no. It's not what it looks like!
It was an accident, really! I swear!
Wait! See, look!
We still have these noodles! They're... jelly noodles.
That's good, right?
I'll have your blood.
Huh? Wh-What was that?
Your blood!
You'll pay for it with your life! Come back!
Uh.
Huh?
I'm so sorry, Mai!
We screwed up the rice and curry, so there's no lunch!
Are you mad at us?
At least we still have these noodles.
You're a life saver!
Be free.
So, uh. Here's our lunch.
One serving of jelly noodles.
We only brought one pack?!
I was thinking we could ration
it out evenly with each other.
But because you and I were the ones who ruined the lunch,
Mai gets first dibs.
Rock, paper, scissors!
Boo-yah!
You better not try anything funny
and eat the entire thing by yourself!
Oh, calm down. I would never do anything mean like that.
Now then, it's time for me to dig in!
Down the wrong pipe.
Grumble...
Grumble.
I know! How 'bout we play some cards!
How 'bout not!
At this rate, the entire trip is gonna be a bust,
so we might as well try and have some
fun playing games and end on a high note!
I got it!
Oh, yeah? What'cha got?
I was just thinking,
when adults get sad and bored,
they like to break out the drinks!
I guess that's true!
Mai! Am I right, or am I right?
I came prepared. One sec.
Whoa, that's super hardcore.
Yeah, you bet I am!
Watch out! We got a badass over here!
Ta-da!
Ugh! I don't care!
I'm gonna chug it!
Don't do it! You'll die, I bet!
Maybe Mai can share whatever she has left!
Huh?
Oh, this? It's cider.
Ah!
Out from the bath, have some milk.
Pretend that you're drunk.
I'm Peso!
Ten-Yen here!
I'm Wado-kaichin!
Remember! Just because you're
currency, doesn't mean you're current!
The next episode of My Ordinary Life is Episode 7.
Look forward to it!