Hm?
I've brought him, sir.
Enter.
Why, if it isn't the great King Albert.
Why you...
Tell me, what's the meaning of this, Dolph?
Oh, calm yourself.
I simply hoped we could enjoy a meal together.
Well, that's a shame.
It seems as though there is no more food left for you.
Restrain him.
Sir.
Huh...
So that's what you were after?!
Now, what do you say we end this game of
hide-and-seek with that princess of yours, King Albert?
Well? Your Majesty?
Did you find her?
Negative!
I'll check this section.
Listen closely, men!
We're only after the wooden cube!
Try not to kill the princess!
Don't think for a single moment you'll
get away with this, Dolph. Hear me?
I already have.
I'm afraid nobody has the power to stop me at this point.
You're out of allies, and out of luck.
What a shame. Right, Albert?
Thank you for this little globetrotting trip of yours.
It was the most perfect
opportunity you could have given me.
With the help of my subordinates, I
was able to trap you and the princess!
But why? What brought upon this betrayal?
It looks like you still don't understand at all.
I'm grateful for everything you've done.
Raising an orphan like me as one of your own,
and even appointing me as the commander of your kingdom.
I don't understand.
Are you really this foolish?
It's because I have my own ambitions.
This is the kind of divine punishment that you deserve.
Accept it.
Lord Dolph!
Huh?
We've located the princess!
Okay! Let's boogie!
Excuse me.
Take this time to think carefully
about your dying words, won't you?
King Albert.
You filthy traitor!
What do you think you're doing?!
Have you all completely lost your minds?
Well, if it isn't Princess Starla herself.
It's so good to see you.
Dolph, you bastard!
You have no freakin' idea what you've done, do you?
What a shame to ruin that pretty
face with such a dirty mouth.
Of course I know what I've done.
I've taken King Albert's precious wooden cube.
And once I get my hands on your cube as well,
I'll be able to revive the ancient weapon.
Then I'll finally be able to ascend
as the new King of the Fey Kingdom!
Struggle all you wish, but no one will save you.
There's nowhere to run anymore!
Now, hand it over peacefully and I might let you live!
Whoa. Dolph is dead!
Hurrah! All hail the Princess, hurrah!
All hail the princess, hurrah!
All hail...
...the princess! Hurrah!
All hail the princess, hurrah!
All hail the princess, hurrah...
You bastards!
You guys all owe me big time!
Now, then! Bring me to my father right away!
Hm? Wait a sec.
Isn't this the item the princess was protecting earlier?
Yeah, then that must mean...
Uh? Wait... what?!
Then, that means...
I could have the power to be king!
No, hang on, let's not get crazy here.
Man, I could really use a cigarette.
After 12 long years of service,
I honestly thought I would live
out the rest of my life as a soldier.
But now... To have a chance like this...
I could never.
I have no reason to become king.
I wouldn't know what to do if I did.
And even with both cubes in my possession,
I couldn't revive that ancient weapon if I tried.
No!
Wha...?!
What a beautiful morning.
All right! I won! I think?
I did! Awesome!
Check it out! I just won a 100,000
yen in this lottery prize thing!
Really?! You gonna treat me to a cut of that or what?
I don't even know what to treat myself with first!
What do I even buy? Like a car or a house or something?
Hang on a sec.
This, uh, is from last year.
Uhh...
Don't sweat it, the lottery is
almost impossible to win, so it's fine.
I know, but it still breaks my heart.
Don't be like that.
You shouldn't be so down on your birthday, so here!
Huh? For real? A present? Thanks so much!
Can I open it now?
Mm-hm. It's really nothing special.
Just something that I had laying around the house.
I'm sure it's great! A gift is a gift!
It's the thought that counts!
Miss Sakurai?
Huh?
Oh, Mr. Takasaki! How are you this morning?
I'm fine, thank you. So, um...
What are you gonna do about that Aioi kid?
She never even attempts to do her assigned homework.
Oh, uh! I, uh... I'm sorry!
I think a nice, stern lecture from her
teacher-slash-counselor would help set her straight.
Uh, sure. I can try.
I'll see if there's something I can do for her.
Now if you'll please excuse me, I have a class.
I'm counting on you!
Excuse me.
I'm so sorry! Are you all right?
I didn't spill any on you, did I?
No, no, I'm perfectly fine.
Don't worry about it!
I just want to protect her!
In my 26 years on this Earth,
I've always had absolutely no luck with women.
But now, feelings for her have sprouted
like a surprise bamboo shoot in the garden.
No, I can't! I'm a professional!
There's no room for romance in the workplace!
I have to pull myself together!
Hm? Huh. Is that...?
Miss Sakurai!
Hm?
Wait, you forgot your black folder.
Oh, thank you so much Mr. Takasaki.
Uh. But I have my materials right here.
Uh.
Mr. Takasaki!
Where do you think you're taking my folder?
Uh! M-My apologies.
Heh! Well then, I have to get going.
I wish I could take her mushroom picking!
Come to think of it... Does she have a boyfriend?
She doesn't wear a ring,
so I can assume that she isn't married.
Does that mean I might still have a chance with her?
I don't even know what kind of music she likes!
What's her favorite animal?
And favorite sport? And vegetable?
Ah! What am I thinking?
Be gone, impure thoughts! I can't be a role-model
to the students if I let my mind wander like this!
Ah, Mr. Takasaki! Let me guess,
you're having trouble with some of your students.
But you know, it should be fine
to ask what her favorite food is.
Hey, Miss Sakurai, what's your favorite thing to eat?
Um, I like a bit of everything.
Ha, ha, ha! Is that so?
How do you feel about shiitake mushrooms?
They're great grilled or boiled!
That's true. And fried too, right?
Of course! Fried is perfectly okay!
I bet those would be pretty tasty.
Yeah, I got this!
Just act natural. It'll be fine if I just talk normally.
Like if I'm talking to eggplants or something.
Nice and calm.
Miss Sakurai?
Yes? How may I help you now?
I'm sorry for bothering you so suddenly like this.
I was just wondering if you
have a boyfriend at the moment.
What the hell am I saying?!
I'm a fool! A complete idiot! An absolute moron!
Nope! Um. I'm single.
Single... Single... Single...
Sprout! Sprout!
Sprout! Sprouting!
Um, Mr. Takasaki?
I'm so sorry if that was too forward!
It worked out all right!
And I wish you the best of luck
with your next class, Miss Sakurai.
Thank you! I wish you the same as well, Mr. Takasaki.
Thanks.
Right, excuse me then. I'll see you later!
I wish you the same as well.
I wish you the same as well...
Well, I see that you're in good spirits today.
Helvetica Standard.
Wait! Please!
Give me back my sickle!
If I don't pawn off this sickle
for food, I'll die from starvation!
Oh no, a dead end!
Well, I'll be.
Please give it back to me!
Oh, man!
♪ First comes a rock, what's it gonna be? ♪
♪ Rock-paper-scissors and a one, two, three! ♪
Wow! I won!
Oh hey, thanks!
And that's not all!
Add the coconut milk.
For tomorrow's forecast.
Miracle's in a pinch!
But I've got more where that came from!
Hey, I bet you I can name something that you've
never ever, ever thought about before in your entire life!
Sure, go ahead.
A quirky office lady's travel diary!
I have a bit.
Uhh...
Hurry!
Looks like the train is gonna leave at any second!
Wait! Hang on!
All right! We're in!
Safe!
You're the only one who made it.
Selamat tinggal .
Right. Um. Let's keep those orders coming in.
Yellowtail, and a Hamachi!
Let's keep those orders coming in.
One tuna and a fluke fin please.
An eel for me.
So, one order of albacore, and...
Heh. I forgot the rest.
Wow, he forgot it all.
Huh?
Hm?
Oh, hello there!
Huh? Uh, yeah, hi?
What do you think you're doing?
Uh. Heh, heh...
Hey, do you mind? Why do you keep doing that?
I can't help it! That thing's so cool and weird!
Huh? What? No, it is not!
It's normal! Keys are a very popular trend right now.
Huh.
How'd you pull that one off, huh?
C'mon, what's your secret! I just wanna see it! Chill out!
Okay. Fine. I'll go.
Bye.
What?
Oh, come on, I was just messing with you!
Well, I didn't care for it.
So can you please give me my arm back?
Huh?
Pick a hand!
It's in your bag!
Hey! You got it!
All right, question number two.
Huh?
If Kenta's mom goes out to the
supermarket and picks up ten apples,
and then eats three of them later that day, and gives
four of the remaining apples to her neighbor Yumiko then
where would you find your missing arm?
In your bag!
Oh, wow! You got another one right!
All I want is my arm, so can you just...?
Only if you get the answer the final question!
If you want this arm, then you gotta earn it!
But why? It was my arm in the first place!
Do you want it back or not?
Yeah, of course I do.
Then let's get started.
First, try saying the word "bag" ten times fast.
Hm?
Bag, bag, bag, bag, bag, bag, bag, bag, bag, bag.
What kind of cloth would you use to clean up a mess?
A bag! No, wait, I mean a rag!
Boop! Boop!
Huh?!
The correct answer was a towel.
No way! That's so unfair!
I'm just playin'.
You're good.
Okay, now can you stop following me around?
All right, I'll stop. Don't worry.
Heh.
Huh. Would ya look at that.
Heh, heh.
It came off!
Finally! It came off!
I'm free!
Huh?
Mio!
Hm?
Hey, I'll walk with you.
Okay. Are you on your way back from class too?
Yeah, Oh, I just met the most interesting person!
Really? Tell me about 'em.
Well, her arm came off.
Huh?
And she had a key in her back.
What?! No way!
I'm not kidding! That's how she was!
Sounds pretty weird to me.
I want people to look at me and think,
"Oh, he looks pretty cool!"
Hey! You ready, Nano?
Okay!
Magic ball!
Well, she is just a child.
Not surprising.
I win!
Aw man, I lost!
What are they doing?
That is not how you play this game.
Sakamoto! How many points did I just get?
What?!
'Kay! It's my turn to throw the ball!
Go!
She hasn't even pitched yet!
Is she trying to kill me with that?
Sakamoto! How many points did I get for that one, huh?
Oh, come on!
She swung again!
You're up. Go get 'em, champ.
How do you expect me to do that? There's
no way hold that bat in these little paws!
Aww...
Unbelievable.
You'd think you would understand
how paws work at this point.
Since you're poking at my pads all the time.
You kids can be so simple-mind... ed...
Aww...
Uh, okay then. Mew-ving on.
The way you kids are playing isn't safe, so, I uh
guess I'll just have to sit here and keep an eye on you.
Why don't you just put the bat down and play catch?
Sure!
You got it, coach!
Coach?
Coach, what do we do if we only have one glove?
I think you'll be fine without one.
Hey, coach! This glove doesn't fit my little hand.
It goes on the other hand like you had it before!
Help us, coach!
C'mon, coach!
Huh?! What would you kids do without me?
Hakase! Here comes the ball!
Bring it!
Oh no, where on earth could it have landed?
And then the teacher totally freaked out at me!
Can't blame him.
Agreed.
You guys really think so?
I think he went a little overboard, personally.
Yeah, maybe, but you gotta watch out from now on.
Yeah, I guess you're right.
It could only get worse from here.
Oh, thank you, sir.
A true gentleman!
So, do mind if I borrow it from ya sometime, Mai, please?
Sure.
Great! You're the best!
I wonder if that's the girl my sister met?
...man I'm starving!
I am a Wooden Cube.
My master can only obtain the ancient
weapon of legend by using my power.
The next episode of My Ordinary Life is Episode 8.
Look forward to it!