I'm telling ya, Daiku Coffee is
pretty great after that remodel they did.
Really?
See? Check it out!
You weren't kidding.
It's like a real café now.
Welcome!
I've already been here, but take as long as
you need to figure out their menu and order.
Oh, really? Okay.
Yeah, lemme get a white chocolate
mochaccino in a grande, please.
Huh?
And if it's not too much trouble, can I get it with
caramel sauce, hazelnut syrup,
extra whip, chocolate chips,
and an additional shot of espresso, affogato style?
Screw this!
Wait! Where are you going?
My previous attempts at researching
Nano Shinonome were unsuccessful.
But luckily, I have a plan!
Now with double the oxidizing
strength, unleashing the power of oxygen,
it'll make my tough problems disappear like magic!
It's Mr. Oxidation Plus!
With this, I'll finally have my chance to study that girl!
For the sake of science!
I don't even know what I wanna study first!
There are so many options.
Maybe I'll start...
See what you can muster!
Oh, no. What do I do?
Whoa. I guess we're working
with these compass things today.
It looks like you're pretty excited to get started, huh?
Uh, sure!
Hey, guys!
Today's class is a study hall now.
Yeah! All right!
I wonder if it's because Ms. Nakamura collapsed again.
She sure does fall over a lot, doesn't she?
Hey, Sasahara!
You're supposed to be on cleaning duty!
I completed the sweeping responsibilities assigned to me.
Uh! But you left a pile of crap on the floor!
Hm. Did I really?
Go back downstairs and finish it up!
I'm curious as to how you knew that
you would be able to find me on the roof.
Don't be stupid! It's a nice day
so I came to enjoy the warm weather,
and you just happened to be up here, okay?
I see.
Sorry for troubling you.
I appreciate you always looking out for me.
Hm.
Don't you dare take it the wrong way!
It's not like I did it for you or anything!
Wow.
It's my day off!
I've got plans to meet up with Mai in the next town over.
She said that there would be free candy
involved if I came, so how could I say no?
Want some bread?
Oh, no thank you, it's fine. I ate earlier, so...
I thought dogs were like, not allowed on trains.
Here.
I'm quite all right.
Look, my stop is coming up,
so I better hop out of my seat
right now and get ready to go!
The next stop is Tokisadametonyamachi.
Good call, Mr. Announcer man!
We've now arrived at Tokisadametonyamachi...
Perfect. Get me off this thing.
So long train-riding people. Yuuko out.
This is fine!
I'm just taking longer for dramatic effect!
I gotta keep my cool!
Once I'm off the train, this'll all be over!
I'm so sorry! I wasn't looking where I was going and...
Come on! Don't sweat it!
I'm in the next town over, and it's
practically a different country here!
I'll never see any of these people ever again,
so it's totally fine!
Is it just me or am I being followed?
I'm just imagining things!
It's pro'bly 'cause I'm still flustered from earlier.
Things will be fine if I focus on
getting to the Daiku Burger place.
Where ever that is.
Well, according to the map Mai gave me...
...this thing is nothing but treble.
I'll just ask for directions. Yeah.
'Scuse me, but do you know how
to get to Daiku Burger from here?
Ah! Okay! That's it! You better stop following me around
or I'm gonna report you for breaking some sort of law!
I'm sure I can find one!
I heard you're looking for the Daiku Burger nearby.
I'm actually meeting somebody there, so I
can show you the way if you need some help.
Welcome!
Hm?
Sorry, Sis. Club ran long today.
You're late!
Looks like she was telling the truth.
Thank you for your patience!
I don't see Mai, so I guess she isn't here yet.
Aw, man.
This has been a day, and it's barely even started!
Oh, well. At least I'm in a different city.
Yeah! I just need to look at the bright side!
I'll learn from what happened here, so
I can be prepared for when it matters!
That's right!
If I can survive this level of humiliation,
I can take on anything the world throws at me!
Yuuko.
Sorry I'm late.
Wait, what? Is that what I think it is?
Trick or treat.
I'm already in this deep. Might as well commit.
I'm all in!
Trick or treat to you, too.
Don't they know Halloween was last week?
"The Life of Crow"! Check it out!
I'm not sleepy enough to sleep right now.
You could always try counting sheep in your imagination.
I've heard that helps.
Okay, I'll try counting sheepies.
One sheepy jumping over a fen...
She fell asleep after one?
Wow, that really works!
Let me try!
One fluffy sheepy...
That sheepy never made it over.
There ya go.
Thanks a lot! You're the best, sis.
Hey, so does that Sasahara guy
teach you how to do stuff like this?
What makes you think that?! Huh?
Why would I ever go to a guy
like that to teach me anything?
I just thought you two seemed close, so...
Well, we're not close, like, at all!
And don't you dare think that we are! You got it?
Uh, sis, you're scaring me.
But if you two aren't close, then
why did you iron his handkerchief?
Uh, that was just something I found on
the ground and wanted to fix up a little.
Did you wanna make it nice because it was Sasahara's?
Yeah, right. I would never do that.
I felt like practicing my ironing, and the
iron just so happened to be out and ready to use
and the handkerchief I found also just
happened to be sitting underneath it.
I guess.
Yeah! It was just circumstance!
Dang. She's so transparent.
That doesn't explain why you looked so
happy ironing something you found on the street.
There's a simple explanation for that!
It... was because...
It's because the Earth must've entered the
Photon Belt at that moment and reality shifted.
You'll never guess what happened!
Yeah? What?
I finally talked to Oono yesterday!
Wow! Really?
Two hours by train. And one hour by bus.
I left behind the hustle of city life.
In its place, I now have the
peacefulness of S Town's countryside.
I searched for so long,
never thinking for a moment that I
would actually be able to find it again.
Yet I never wavered.
I continued my quest for that one special book.
It brought a spark of color and
excitement into my heart when I was a child.
Coloring the gray, uneventful days of my youth.
This is the place. The library.
At last... I can see it once more.
Fate was kind enough to bring me and this book together.
And fate has my thanks.
While trying to ignore my racing heart...
...slowly...
...I open up the cover.
Time's almost up, so finish what you can,
and don't forget to put your name on the top
before you turn it in.
Ten, nine, eight, seven.
Uh?
Six... Five...
And four... And three...
Two...
And one...
Zero!
Okay. Everybody pass your papers up to the front.
You do know that Halloween is over already, right?
Helvetica Standard.
Gross! I wanted to like this
coffee, but it's not very coffee-y.
You wanna run that one by me again? It's not coffee-y?
I can't really think of any
other way to explain how it tastes!
It's simply not coffee-y enough!
Here, try it and you'll see what I mean! Come on!
Okay. I don't see the big deal, it's just coffee, right?
It's not coffee-y enough.
Hop! Hop! H...!
Hop!
Hey, guys! I finally finished my latest project!
Look, Biscuit #2!
I'm Biscuit #2.
Oh. It's that thing.
Okay. Ouch.
Come on! Don't ignore him like that!
Um, but I've already seen this one before.
He's not a "one," he's a "two," and that's different!
He's way cooler than before!
Sure.
My name is Biscuit #2.
I was made by Hakase Shinonome, and I'm a biscuit robot!
As my name implies, I run solely on biscuits.
Biscuits are like fuel. They give me life.
Hakase, I require a biscuit at once!
Wha...?
But this is the last one and I wanna eat it.
Huh?
Biscuit #2's special skill is speed reading!
Check it!
I'm finished.
Done.
Uhh...
Why aren't you excited, Nano?!
Well, it's just that I can speed read also.
Then how come you always read so slow?!
Explain that!
Um, I enjoy taking my time with books.
It makes me feel like I'm
reading them like a normal person!
Yawn.
Now what seems to be the problem, Biscuit #2?
Looking at all of these tiny
letters is kinda making me sleepy.
That's how a normal person reads.
Why don't you ever say how amazing I
am when I do all this awesome stuff?!
Oh, wow, I had no idea it would make you that upset.
I'm not upset, you are!
If it helps, I've always thought
what you do is pretty impressive.
I'm pretty impressive, but you don't
have to make such a big deal out of that.
I don't know if I'm the one that's making it a big deal.
Okay!
So tell me more about how impressive I am!
You're as impressive as a mountain range!
I don't know what that means, so try again.
'Kay. You have an incredibly vast knowledge!
Like it's big? As big as what?
How 'bout as big as a whale?
Oh, I like the sound of that!
Whales are pretty big, huh?
They're the biggest!
Never say something is good enough.
Never say "this is good enough."
"That's good enough."
So, what do you plan on doing?
Play a board game!
What's your act gonna be?
I'm doing an exciting, yet
intellectually stimulating, quiz game!
Entertaining the princess for prize money
seems like a great way to pass the time,
and it can end up being kinda fun.
Feels nice to enjoy ourselves and
take a break from all the serious stuff.
Yeah! For sure.
I'm sure you all thought you knew where the ball was.
But in reality, it's under here.
Not bad, #66!
That's quite the hidden talent you got goin' there.
Heh. To be honest, my dream is to
become the Royal Magician someday.
I'd say that dream might become a reality soon!
I hope so!
All right! I'm getting pumped!
Let's get this thing started already!
Men! The time has come!
Silence!
We'll now proceed in the order
indicated by the slips you drew.
Whoever drew one, come forward.
That would be me!
Whoa, #66 right off the bat!
Looks like this will start with a bang.
The Royal Magician, huh?
Embrace your dreams, 66!
Now, go ahead and guess which cup has the...
I just wanted to be a Royal Magician!
Next.
Whoever drew two, step forward!
My turn now.
It's time to show the world what I can do!
I'll make a name for myself right here!
Hey. Who's that?
It's him, Funny 4! If anyone can do it, he can!
I am #4, here to entertain.
Next.
I can't believe 4 failed.
Hey, you doin' all right?
I'm up next.
Huh? Wait, aren't you the quiz guy?
I'm so screwed.
But I don't have a choice. The quiz game's all I've got.
But if I make it easy enough,
maybe it'll appease the princess
and I won't fall to my doom.
It'll be fine.
As long as she gets the answers right...
I'll just give her simple, easy-to-solve questions.
Uh, #6! And I'm here to give you a quiz!
Can you name something that has the
word "bread" in it but is also inedible?
Uh, it's a multiple choice question!
Uh, The first option is breadbox
and the second option is melon bread!
Wow, that's easy!
Ah!
I give up.
That is... the correct secret answer!
My whole life, I regretted nothing.
Except this!
We're so dead.
Even the quiz master was sent packing.
Next.
Um, I'm #7!
And I can recite every location
the Olympics have ever taken...
We'll never forget your courage, #7.
What's the matter?
Is no one here capable of entertaining the princess?
What am I gonna do?
And here I thought a cheerleading
routine would be a good idea.
Speak for yourself!
I was splitting chopsticks with my butt cheeks!
I was gonna dance with a sushi mat!
I thought I'd be cool to shred a cabbage!
We're all doomed. Every last one of us.
Relax.
You didn't forget that you have me around, did ya?
Wait! You're the...
His harlequin antics have made him the best clown in town.
There's nobody funnier than this guy.
He's... Harlequeen 13!
I'll turn those frowns upside-down and
put on an unforgettable show in the process.
Boom!
Hang on a sec, 13!
I dunno what you have planned, but it's suicide!
Do you honestly think I would dance
Swan Lake or something stupid like that?
Just watch and learn.
I'll show you why they call me the Harlequeen 13...
Harlequeen 13!
Huh?! Why am I fall...?!
Next, #5.
Don't make me say it twice! Come on out!
Who drew that one? Who is #5?
Is that you?
No! That's just what it says on my hat!
Who is it then?
Not me!
Hang on. Aren't you #5?
Yeah. He's dead.
Number 5 had better step forward immediately!
What is the hold up?
Huh?
I knew it!
Next. I don't care who it is. Just go.
What do we do now?
We're all...
...completely screwed!
We could have a thousand more men
and it still wouldn't make a difference!
I've had enough of this stupid game!
And I won't watch this anymore!
I'll go stand in the hallway.
I'm a white chocolate mochaccino with
caramel sauce, hazelnut syrup, extra whip,
chocolate chips on top, and
an additional shot of espresso,
affogato style, in a grande size!
The next episode of My Ordinary Life is Episode 19!
Look forward to it!