Helvetica Standard.
Come on, you two.
When are you gonna get around to paying rent?
You're up to 60,000 yen now!
I'm so sorry.
I don't want apologies! I want my money!
Last time, you said you'd be able to pay the
rent in full the next time I came around for it.
Well, next time is now, so cough it up!
There's no use stone-walling me in this situation.
I'm not leaving without your rent.
Um...
This is all a poor sparrow can spare.
One: Meso-American Slider.
Two: Western Box Turtle.
Three: Red-Bellied, Short-Necked Turtle.
It's two.
The answer is... number three.
Great job, everyone.
Whatever.
Hey, what are you still doing up at this hour?
Is your cold gone?
Mh-hm.
Then you should be good to go back to school tomorrow.
Your tests are coming up soon.
Fine.
You've been out for three whole days, so you're
gonna have to catch up on your homework quickly.
See if you can borrow your friends' notes from class.
I better not see you bring home
another failing score like the last time.
You hear me?
Aw, come on, Mom! It's fine!
My finals don't even start until, like... tomorrow!
I totally forgot!
Why didn't you remind me?
You were much too sick to study anyway, so I let you rest.
Nuh-uh! I'd study in my sleep!
Would you really?
I wouldn't!
That's what I thought.
You didn't even bring it up,
I couldn't even try to study!
Would you have studied if you'd known?
I guess not!
If you fail your exams, I'll kill you.
You don't have to go that far!
I'm super, ultra, great, delicious, wonderfully screwed.
Well, it looks like I have no choice.
The next school day starts in T-minus ten hours!
Luckily, tomorrow's tests are just for English and music.
In that case, I'll focus on English tonight.
'Kay, I just have to ignore all of my
natural lazy-person instincts and concentrate.
I won't procrastinate!
So that I can live on without regret.
So that I can laugh in each coming day.
Even through all the tears and sweat.
Even though obstacles stand in my way.
I will never give up.
I want to keep a smile on my face.
I am like a ship crossing the sea.
Sailing for the light where I want to be.
On a straight track.
Breaking the chains which hold me back.
Becoming my best self!
By Yuuko.
Perfect. I'm done...
...with a poem.
Things we think are freakin' cool!
It's nothing special. Fuggedaboudit.
The shy smile of a local mechanic!
It's go time.
I dunno what's gonna be on the
test, so I have to take it all in!
All right, vocab, come on!
Bring it!
Attempt: To make an effort.
Love: To earn my heart.
Always: We were always apart.
Confirmation: Your love is like.
Teleportation: It crosses even time, so.
Cosmos: Sailing through star and sky.
A midnight submarine: I want to ride with you.
Forever, with you.
Forever, eternally.
Forever, until the end.
I'm done! With another poem!
Ugh! It's over! I'm screwed!
No matter how hard I try, I can't study!
I'm so dead! My mom is gonna kill me!
Why did I have to get over my
stupid cold today of all days?
Being sick is way better than taking a test
that I'm doomed to fail!
If only I could be sick for a just little longer!
I got it.
My plan is completely foolproof!
Yup.
If I wanna get out of the test,
I'll make myself sick again!
It stings! But I gotta push through the pain!
My body is still weak from beating my last cold,
so I bet I'll be running a fever in no time.
Come on, come on! Just a little more.
If I can tough this out now, then
it'll all be worth it in the end!
The path will open!
If I can get a fever, then I'm all set!
I'll have some shaved ice for good measure.
I'll blast the AC, too!
And go to sleep on top of the covers!
Why do I have to be so freakin' healthy?
Yuuko! It's time to get up!
Last resort.
Thermometer... plus match...
...equals fever on-demand!
Are you up yet?
You're going to school today, right? Yuuko?
It burns! It burns!
What are you doing?
Mom, I got a fever!
Guess I must've gotten sick again.
How bad is it?
Uh. Well, lemme see.
Huh? It's 88.8 degrees.
What?
Now look at what you did! You broke it!
No, I didn't! I got sick again, I swear!
You seem perfectly healthy to me.
Yeah, It's probably because
there was something in the water.
Thanks, man.
I had no idea that today was the
last day to turn in our application.
One more day and the club would've been a goner.
But even if you turn in the form on time,
won't the club still get shut
down for the lack of members?
Nah, I wouldn't worry about that.
Tell ya what, how 'bout I bring
you some juice tomorrow as a thanks.
You don't have to do that. It's all good.
It's no problem at all! See ya!
Hey, I need to stop and buy a juicer
and an apple orchard on the way home.
Yes, sir.
Ah. So that's the power of the Daiku Group.
No string left.
I won't be able to tie together a straw doll to
put in the Principal's locker if I don't have any.
And what's worse,
it looks like I don't even have the straw to craft with,
nor do I have any money to buy any.
My wife handles the money, but she's gone.
We're all out of rice and I'm hungry.
At times like these, a swig of brandy would come in handy,
but my liver couldn't take it.
My favorite team lost, and for whatever
reason, the cheeseburger I ordered earlier
didn't have any cheese on it.
The visitor counter on the home page
of my website hasn't budged at all,
and not a single person logged on to
my usual online chat group yesterday.
That empty chat room reminds me.
When I got on to the bus the other day,
everyone else got off and left me alone.
And that empty bus reminds me.
I went on a field trip back in high school.
Time for bed.
And just a couple of minutes
after we turned off the lights...
Who else is awake?
I asked everyone, but they were already asleep.
And speaking of sleep,
I haven't been getting much of it lately.
Since I can't get any rest,
I ended up snacking through the night,
and I've wound up putting on some weight.
And speaking of food,
I got a present for my birthday last month.
But it was just a roll of bread.
This is no good!
All of this negative thinking is getting me nowhere!
What I really need to do is
remember the good things in life.
Who could that be?
Yes?
Oh-ho!
Kimiko!
Mom is still away on her trip, right?
I thought I'd come by and make dinner.
I see. Well, thank you.
Hi, Grandpa!
Hello there, Mi.
Oh. Looks like you've grown taller, huh?
Just what I needed.
I'll spend some time with my grandson,
who hasn't a care in the world.
Guess what, Grandpa?
Hm?
I made a dumpling when I was at the park earlier.
You can have it if you want!
That so?
You're hungry, so you should eat it!
How sweet.
It's real chocolate, so you're gonna like it!
Oh, can I really? Well, thank you.
What's with the water works?
I guess you've always been the sensitive type.
'Kay, I'll be in the kitchen if you need me.
Okay.
That's right.
There's no point in focusing on
all of the negative things in life.
I made it with love just for you, grandpa!
Come on, hurry up!
Eat the dumpling! It's yummy, I promise!
Well, uh, this is...
Eat it! What are you waiting for?
You should eat it! It's tasty!
I'm sure.
Somehow, happiness tastes just about as good as dirt.
Hey, Mom? Grandpa fell down.
Your order. Thanks for waiting.
There is nothing...
nothing greater than peace.
Trying to kill me?
It's finished!
What's up?
Super-duper glue!
That is quite large.
Because it's super-duper.
I'm gonna spread this so Nano and Sakamoto
will get here stuck when they least expect it.
What kind of prank are you tryin' to pull now?
You're being so obvious no one is gonna fall for your...
Gotcha!
You got me in what?
Hey! Get this stuff off of me!
I've got things to do, ya know!
It'll only come off with water.
Then go get some water and set me free!
Hold on, it's snack time.
Hey!
Since it's snack time, I need to
go to the kitchen, so see ya for now.
No!
My feet. Hang on.
Oh, no. Uh.
Hey.
Do something. This sucks.
Heh. You look like a bug who got stuck in a glue trap.
What are you laughing at?
You're stuck in here, too!
Uh. Oh, that's right.
Serves you right!
That's some karma for ya!
That's weird. I-I can't get out.
It's your own fault for being such a troublemaker.
I've fallen and I can't get up.
Hang on. Where'd Sakamoto go?
Kitty-kitty? Kitty-kitty?
There you are!
This won't come off without water.
I won't be able to eat snacks if I'm stuck here.
What if I'm stuck to the floor for a
really long time and get super hungry?
I won't be able to eat my snacks.
Am I'm gonna starve?
I don't wanna become a skeleton.
I'm actually dying here.
Hello! I'm back!
It's Nano!
I'm happy to be home.
It's so hot out there and... What happened?
How'd you end up like that?
Well, I put down this glue!
Just like that! And it got all sticky-like!
But then I tripped and fell,
and got stuck in it, and now I need water, and I need...
Water?
That's right!
You should really get up off the floor first.
And then we should get this mess cleaned up before...
Huh? What is this stuff?
Hey! Uh.
How did he...? Here, I'll, uh...
Oh, no! My hand came off!
I don't understand what's happening!
Oh, no! My other hand!
President.
So this is the true power of the Daiku Group.
Ha. Well, that sure was a lovely rainbow we just saw.
Hey! Guess who!
Well, is it Hakase?
Yay, that's correct! Good job. How'd you know?
I mean, it's kinda obvious. No one else lives here, so...
Okay! Now it's your turn to play, Nano!
Huh? All right then.
Hey! Guess who!
You! Nano!
It's another peaceful day at the Shinonome household.
Hey, Nano! I was right, right?
Uh, yeah. You were.
Great! I get to go again now!
So turn around!
Sure.
This is bad. So bad.
Really bad!
I'm still stuck on the first stupid question!
What is this thing?
It looks like some sort of low-level monster or something.
But how do I describe that in one word?
Wait, I've seen this. But where?
I think I asked Ms. Sakurai about it before, but when?
Let's see.
What is this supposed to be?
No, I'm not asking about the answer.
I'm wondering if you were the one who
drew this low-level-looking monster.
That's it! I did ask about this dude!
I don't remember what she said!
Just calm down! I need to breathe.
If I panic, I won't be able to think straight!
All right, focus. What is this thing doing?
Flying? Was that it?
No, it can't be.
This little guy is so distracting!
Why can't I stop focusing on this monster?
Wait, monster?
This isn't just testing my language skills.
It's testing my sanity.
But this is the best I can do, so I should just move on.
So what's next?
It's the same monster swinging a tennis racket!
Which means the first answer is definitely not monster.
Why is this thing torturing me?
I'll just erase my first answer and start over.
Where is my eraser?
Every dang thing in my stupid life sucks!
What do I do now? This is so bad!
Do I just have to live with my mistakes?
Mai! You saved me!
I'm so glad we're friends! Best friends!
A sand eraser?
I can't use this! It'll rip my paper!
That defeats the purpose!
I don't have time to worry about that!
I need to see if Mai has a...
She went to sleep!
Uh. All right, ten minutes remaining!
My time! It's ticking away!
Come on, I gotta calm down.
That's right.
I have to relax... and just clear my mind.
Purge all thought. Be free.
Okay. And time's up!
No!
It's raining.
Only in my heart.
Good morning, sir!
Yes, good morning!
No way! I just got a love letter!
Are you for real? Who sent it?
It says it's from Tanaka in Class Four!
Come on! Open it already!
Don't rush me!
I'm a dirt ball.
I'm an iron ball!
I'd tell you a joke, but none of mine are clean.
And I shall strike when the iron is hot!
Clang-clang!
The next episode of My Ordinary Life is Episode 12.
Look forward to it!