Okay, the testing period is over.
Yay!
Whoa. That's quite the celebration.
They must be relieved after putting so much
effort into their studies. It warms my heart.
♪ The test is over! And it was a snap! ♪
My life flashed before my eyes. Am I
dreaming? Pinch me as hard as you can!
We finished! Nothing can hurt you now.
My parents are sending each and every
one of you a bag of rice as a gift!
Yeah! Thanks rice man!
The two of us are getting married!
Wow!
Come on! All together now!
Hip-hip...
Hooray!
What the...? Could you not?
This is overkill!
Hooray! Hooray!
Ah, Mio. Good morrow.
No, this is all wrong!
You're supposed to say something like,
"Huh? Uh. The heck is that?"
Be surprised!
Aw, you're not still mad at me, are you?
Can't you just admit it was kinda funny?
I made your mont blanc a Knight.
Nah, I still could've eaten it
if I took that chess piece out,
so it really wasn't that big of a deal.
Yeah, right!
Sis! Why?!
How could you do that to me?!
I was so looking forward to my dessert, and you knew it!
Why did you have to stick a knight on the top?!
I guess... I thought it'd look cool.
Head!
You'd think she'd be used to
my practical jokes at this point.
Gah, she's so annoying.
They only make ten of those mont blancs a day.
Not that it matters.
Cause even if she knew that,
she's always pulling stuff like this.
I thought now that she's in college,
she'd finally understand when to stop.
But whatever, it's fine.
I can let it slide for today, because I've got
better things to do. And she has absolutely no idea!
I knew she'd be up to something, so I was ready.
I disguised my shortcake, so it's safe and sound.
Ahh!
Checkmate! She got me!
I can't believe she freakin' got me!
The strawberry!
She stole the crown jewel of my rare,
only-five-made-per-day gourmet shortcake!
Don't you worry, Strawberry! I'm coming for you!
Hold on!
Where is it?
What did you do to my precious, delicious, sweet...?!
Namaste.
Gut!
Why are you so mean to me?
A shortcake without the strawberry isn't special anymore!
Now it's just a stupid, normal piece of shortcake!
♪ Happy birthday to me, happy birthday to me ♪
♪ Happy birthday dear Yoshino ♪
♪ Happy birthday to me ♪
Sis...
Mio.
Today isn't even your birthday!
I've been wanting to try this place for forever!
And didn't you see it in a magazine?
Sure did.
And it came with a coupon!
No point in showing it to me.
I'm having the Herring Soba.
Ah, hot dish in this weather? You connoisseur.
With no herring.
Then that's just noodles in water!
Ah...
Ah-hem. And what're you going to get, Mio?
I think I'm gonna get the Zaru Soba.
Ah, the classic pick for a non-foodie That's a safe one.
It's good enough for me. What're you getting?
I think I'm gonna have myself
the Summer Veggie Tempura Special.
It's pretty bold to go with a rice dish at a noodle place.
Right?
Yeah, if you say so.
You get it! It's a seasonal item, too.
This kind of dish is special, so
you never know when it'll be back.
Probably next summer.
Maybe you don't get it.
Haven't you ever heard of living in the moment, Mio?
What matters most is the here and now!
Oh, really?
I'm sure you'll understand what I mean one day.
Yeah, okay.
Excuse me!
What would you like to order?
One Herring Soba, a Zaru Soba,
and... the seasonal... special dish...
Herring Soba, Zaru Soba, and a Summer Veggie
Tempura Special. I'll be back with your order soon.
I heard they make all of their
soba noodles by hand at this place.
Can't get any more authentic than that!
Oh, I wonder what this buckwheat dumpling thing is.
It's the squishy stuff they make using the soba flour!
Wow, for real?
Thank you for waiting.
This is the Herring Soba here,
and the order of the Zaru Soba for you.
I don't mind if you guys start
eating your food without me!
If you're sure...
Before it gets cold.
But mine's supposed to be cold.
It must be because my order is from the seasonal menu.
I bet they're taking extra time and care to make it!
Your food is taking a while.
Guess they need extra time to fry all those vegetables.
Or maybe they went out to pick 'em, so they're fresh!
That's it! No wonder they're slow!
I think you could order your food a la carte here too.
Hm, really?
Finally!
Another table's.
Too bad.
God Dammit!
Hey! Just settle down, Yuuko!
How can I?! This is taking freakin' forever!
I don't care if they're famous, even if they
capture the flavors, they'll never capture my feelings!
You're not making any sense!
They're gonna feel my wrath!
Thank you for waiting.
'Bout time! Do you know how long I...
Uh, thanks.
You guys can like, read a book or something.
This might take a little bit.
Things we think are freakin' cool!
Uh.
Young chess players!
I've got my mosquito repellent going,
but I thought it'd be doing more than it is.
They won't leave in the late night.
Mogami River.
Ha!
Ha! Huh! H'ya!
Well, it looks like you're just
minding your own business anyway.
Guess I'll go crawl back into bed then.
Sneak attack!
Victory!
Bug off!
I have taken a precious life.
I'll do it again!
I hit! And I smack!
But they never learn their lesson!
But what else can I do? I'm running out of options!
Listen, Mom!
We can't live in this infested house anymore!
We just have to move! Now!
Do you have any idea what time it is?!
Now shut up and go to sleep!
Helvetica Standard.
Chirashizushi. You try.
Tsurasuzusu.
No! Chi-ra-shi-zu-shi!
Go!
Tsu-ra-su-zu-su.
No, no! Chi.
Chi.
Ra.
Shi.
Zu.
Yes! Chirashizushi. Go!
Tsurasuzusu.
Sakamoto! Check it out!
The bottom of this popsicle says I'm a winner!
See, look at it!
You really shouldn't be eating that right now.
Why can't I eat it?!
Well because, it's gonna spoil your appetite.
Yummy!
I don't get why you got so worked up
over a popsicle stick. You're such a child.
It wasn't a normal stick!
I won it upside-down!
Doesn't matter which way the stick is going when the
outcome's the same. So, you found out two bites earlier.
Big deal.
Seriously. You kids can be so easy to please.
You get excited over the smallest things.
It's a crab!
They never show up! It's like one in a million!
I'm gonna save you for last, little guy!
Thank you very much for the meal.
What's this?
You've barely eaten any your food, Hakase.
Let me guess, you had snacks this afternoon, didn't you?
I'm not proud of it.
How many times have I told you not to snack before meals?!
All gone.
All gone?!
You ate a whole month's worth of snacks?!
That wasn't a compliment!
What am I gonna do with you.
I only did it because Sakamoto told me to!
Is that true?!
Sakamoto said food gets yucky
faster in the summer so I had to do it.
I didn't mean you had to eat all of them.
Snacks go in the tummy. Where else would I put them?
What kind of argument is that?
Sakamoto!
Why are you even considering her side?
If you look at it objectively, the
situation's pretty black-and-white!
But you only have black fur.
That's true.
Uh, what does that have to do with anything?
That's enough.
There's no point in arguing anymore.
I've decided...
Hakase won't be getting her strawberry juice.
Uh. I won't eat anymore snacks!
I said no.
I'll give you my winning popsicle stick!
I don't want it!
I'll eat all of my vegetables!
You better!
Hmph.
I'll take the key off your back!
I'll let it slide this one time.
But next time, no snacks for a month. I mean it.
Okay!
So...
Wait, if I give it to her now,
I feel like our deal is gonna fall through.
You can have your juice after
you take the key off my back.
Ahh!
Fine then. Gimme a sec.
Huh? 'Kay!
Hakase!
Your right hand's a loser.
How did you even come up with this?!
Not a compliment!
I'd appreciate it if you stopped messing with me.
Could you please consider my feelings for a change...
You're not listening!
Rock, paper, scissors!
Mine!
If you look hard enough,
you can find anything.
Oh, Mio! I'm glad you're here.
What do you want, Yoshino?
Something came up, and I was wondering...
I said I'd help out the neighborhood association.
Would you please take my place?
Huh? Why don't you ask Mom instead of me?
Oh, she's busy playing kick volleyball with her
friends. To say thanks, I'll pay you 10,000 yen.
I'm counting on you!
I guess I could use the money.
Not like I'm doing anything anyway.
Think I should try a Mohawk fade with some dreads?
Check it out! That's so cute!
I've been bamboozled!
This whole thing sucks! What am I even doing?!
How did this happen? Why did I agree to this?
Come and get your delicious...
The neighborhood association's big
plan was to sell daifuku on the street?
And with just two people?
Nah, I'll pass.
It's embarrassing!
No wait...
It's too embarrassing!
Everyone's staring at me like I'm an idiot!
How am I supposed to draw people in when I'm
dressed like their weird Daifuku-Dude mascot?
There aren't even any facial features.
It's just a plain, white ball for a head!
What even makes this mascot a dude, anyway?
It's just a big daifuku !
Come to think of it, this Daifuku Fair...
...doesn't seem fair to me!
Uh. I'm sorry...
Sweetie! It's okay! This is the absolute worst.
Whoa! What's that thing?
It looks gross!
Take this, gross thingy!
Stop it, please! That kinda hurts, so cut it out!
Seriously! I mean it! There's no padding in this costume!
Okay, it's starting to really hurt, so please!
Could you just...
Cut it out!
Ah! She's mad! Run for it!
Yeah! Let's get outta here!
What a freaky freak!
Could this get any worse?
Huh?
Yuuko!
Stop tarnishing the Daifuku reputation.
I can't watch. Hand it over.
I'll show you!
Useless part-timers!
Don't just stand there.
Go and work behind the counter.
'Kay?
Yeah...
I swear. This 10,000 yen better be worth it.
♪ Tokachi! Azuki beans! ♪
Can I leave?
♪ Wasanbon sugar! ♪
I just wanna go home.
Well, I guess these daifuku look
pretty nice, but are they even gonna sell?
Excuse me.
How much for one of these?
A customer!
It's, uh...
I have no idea.
Uh, sir! How much does one daifuku...
Maybe this was a bad idea.
I couldn't run even if I tried! I'm strawberry filled!
Uh, yeah.
You could just take it for free.
Cool! Lucky me!
Ha!
It's another peaceful day at the Shinonome household.
Greetings! I'm the King!
Check me out! Looks like I'm pretty isolated.
I better find my chess mates soon!
The set is missing a major piece!
Hope it doesn't get pawned off!
The next episode of My Ordinary Life is Episode 10!
Look forward to it!