[PEASANT A sighs]
[hooves clomping]
[PEASANTS]
Huh?
Our lord travels
in high fashion.
Have a good journey, my lord!
[ALLISTER chuckles]
My goodness, contessa!
How'd an Elf make his
way into the carriage?
[laughs]
[SAINT GERMI] Remind me why
you insisted on coming along?
[ALLISTER]
Don't be like that, contessa!
Hogging them would
be such a cruelty!
[FULAME] We want to see those
scrumptious little Elves too!
[ALLISTER]
Not to ruin the mood, but...
[SAINT GERMI]
Hm?
I can't help but
assume the Drifters'
next target will be
the town of Gadolka.
The Dwarves imprisoned therein
would make for valuable allies.
[FULAME]
Mm...
Gadolka's the largest armory
within the Orte Empire.
I'm sure it's well-guarded.
Those Drifters are a saucy lot.
If only all the kingdom's
adversaries were
this intriguing.
If they take that town though,
the fall of Orte will be
a foregone conclusion.
[ORTE SOLDIER A] All of these
weapons go to the western front?
That's right. Seeing as
how our supply fleet
got sent to the
bottom of the sea.
Took a lot of Orte steel down
with 'em when they sank.
All we can do is ramp up
production to fill the loss.
The Dwarves are gonna have to
work faster than ever before.
Easier said than done,
I would wager.
[ORTE SOLDIER A] If we push
them any harder then we do now,
they'll drop like flies.
[ORTE SOLDIER B] Wouldn't be
the first we've worked to death.
[BOTH]
Huh?
What the hell?
Damn it all!
Did the mine collapse?
[NOBUNAGA] The night-soil
from the latrines,
a little sulfur from Boob Dream,
and some charcoal.
The perfect combination...
...for raining hell upon a foe!
Everything's going up!
Are we under attack?
[BOTH yell]
[ORTE SOLDIERS scream]
[NOBUNAGA] Flame and shrapnel
have their use, but those
explosions give us something
far simpler to exploit.
Time for battle!
Make sure the bastards
can hear you!
Hit them with all your rage,
then take them down!
[ELVES yelling]
[NOBUNAGA]
When met with the chaos
of such an assault on
the senses... men break.
Whether cannon-fire
or a flaming arrow,
the effect is ever the same.
Toyohisa's clan was the first
to copy the foreigner's guns.
Clearly, their knowledge
serves him well!
Kill them all!
[ELVES yelling]
[ORTE SOLDIER B] That yelling!
We're under attack!
[ORTE SOLDIER C]
Is it the Elves?
Damn those Long-Ears!
Get ready!
[ORTE SOLDIER D]
Bastards, all of 'em!
[ALL gasp]
Wait. What the hell is that?!
[chuckles] Bulls-eye!
[ELF A grunts]
What a terrible concoction.
The fruits of our labors are a
devilish substance, to be sure!
See that you pour
that stuff with care!
I'd hate for you to
blow us all to pieces!
Don't lose heart, my friends.
Just handle it
with a light touch
and fire it straight
into their ranks!
[ORTE SOLDIERS screaming]
[NOBUNAGA] I knew explosive
arrows would suffice,
but Yoichi and the Elves
have outdone themselves.
Who would've
thought that archers
could be the agents
of such destruction?
Kind of a shame how all those
weapons are burning to cinders.
We could've cut
through the Orte
with their own stolen steel.
Hell, it's a rout either way.
But it would've been
nice to have 'em.
What the hell's going on?
I don't know, dammit!
Sow panic in their ranks!
Cut them down
with their own fear!
Fire's all around us!
There's no getting away!
We're cut off!
[ELF B]
Run! They have us surrounded!
Every man for himself!
Help us!
So, what now?
Damned if I know!
[NOBUNAGA] Don't give your
enemy a chance to regroup!
Turn them into corpses!
We've already lost! Run for it!
Hold on!
Forward, men! Conquer the town!
Then onward to the castle!
[ELVES yelling]
[ORTE COMMANDER] Within sits
Orte's largest smithy, which we,
the Armored Guard Corp, have
pledged our lives to defend!
You have gained nothing
by your insolence,
but destruction!
[TOYOHISA] Heavy armor,
heavy swords, and heavy spears.
All on foot. No bows. No arrows!
Full retreat!
[ORTE COMMANDER]
Running away? I think not!
[KAFET] I do hope Olmine
is doing all right.
[HARUAKIRA]
Worry not.
Those Japanese Drifters
are industrious.
We don't call her "Olmine of
the Stone Coffins" for nothing,
as they'll soon discover.
[HARUAKIRA] Her casting of
the "Stone Wall" spell is...
...a thing of beauty.
[HARUAKIRA]
Among your coterie,
she's probably been blessed
with more talent than anyone.
Blessed with curves, as well.
Sir, you're such a letch.
Spoken like the dirty old
man you actually are.
[ORTE COMMANDER]
Huh? Where'd it come from?
Toss them over!
[ORTE COMMANDER gasps]
[ORTE SOLDIERS scream]
Their Armored Guard Corp
has been wiped out
and we didn't lose a man!
Onward!
[ORTE SOLDIER E]
Our heavy infantry, dead!
[ORTE SOLDIER F]
No, this isn't happening!
Quickly! Close up the gate!
Close the gate!
[NOBUNAGA] Genius using
the walls to hem them in.
Well played,
Toyohisa, you sly fox.
He took sorcery
meant for defense
and used it to
annihilate the enemy.
I'm sure he wasn't actually
born on a battlefield,
but you'd never know
it to watch him fight.
All the ferocity in the world
won't open that gate, though.
[HANNIBAL munching]
You like those raspberries,
graybeard?
They're tasty.
[NOBUNAGA] Why did he
bother coming with us?
This addled old barbarian
is nothing but dead weight.
[HANNIBAL]
Hey, one-eye.
[NOBUNAGA]
Hm?
Hmph.
[NOBUNAGA]
Quick, now! Get a messenger!
I need to reach Olmine!
[MASHA]
Uh... Right!
[NOBUNAGA]
Clever. How did you...?
[HANNIBAL] Why's it empty?
I want more, dammit!
I told you, that was all of 'em.
Carthage'll fall if
I don't get raspberries.
[MASHA]
Here, sir.
I need to send a message out.
How's this suppose to help?
Olmine said if we talk into it,
she'll be able to hear us.
Hey! Swole-mine! Hey! Can you
hear me over that chest?
[OLMINU]
Shut up, you!
Call me by name, damn it!
[NOBUNAGA]
Whatever! You knew who I meant!
You still have some
wall charms, right?
Proceed as I tell you,
and our forces will be
inside without delay!
Hurry! It's closing!
And not a moment too soon!
The hell did they use to
make explosions like that?
All I know is,
I lit the signal fire.
We probably won't see
reinforcements for half a day.
But with the gate shut tight,
there's no way they're
getting in before then.
They'll be trapped against the
very walls they want to breach.
It looks like the soldiers
outside of the gate
are losing their courage.
[ORTE SOLDIER G]
Are we all that's left?
Damn those Long-Ears!
Soon as the reinforcements
show up, they're all dead!
[ALL gasp]
[MARK] It's like they're
making a staircase!
Nobunaga! You're not going
to believe it! Take a look!
[NOBUNAGA] Sure, the wall
charms are valuable,
but they can't hold a candle
to what this sphere can do.
Why dispatch a rider when you
can speak to the recipient
in the blink of an eye?
This device could
change the world,
but the magicians treat
it like any other tool.
They remain blind
to its potential,
accustomed as they are to them.
They just see
this miraculous ball
as a way to file their daily
reports from the field.
The thought that these spheres
could let armies coordinate
their attacks from afar
never even entered their heads.
They await.
Let's not disappoint them!
[NOBUNAGA] Same goes
for their wall charms.
Olmine will cast them to
shield Toyohisa from danger,
but he'd rather use one
to leap towards it.
Even now, he breaches
the castle with them.
Maybe that is our strength.
As outsiders, we see chances
to which they are blind.
What do we know of
the Ends, though?
Of their strength?
Are we only here to make
war upon each other?
[NOBUNAGA] We fight, but the
endgame is a riddle to us.
[MURASAKI]
You're right. You are outsiders.
Which means you and your fellow
Drifters see things that,
for good or ill,
the others cannot.
Go and turn the old
world on its head.
Without change, there can
be nothing but atrophy.
Break the paradigm as
only you can, Drifters.
The castle belongs to us now!
[ORTE SOLDIERS shouting]
Milord, let's free the
Dwarves right away.
Huh?
Ever since we were young,
we've been told how fiercely
the Dwarves used to fight.
Make no mistake,
my people despise them.
Our fathers would tell
dark tales of the Dwarves
to make us behave.
But at its heart.
the Elves were jealous
of all that which we lack.
Their strength.
Their dogged perseverance.
The axes they hefted
with such ease.
Who knows how many of
them are held captive here?
Before now, the thought
of our people ever being
brothers-in-arms
was inconceivable!
But the day has come!
Better late than never, right?
Let's get to it!
[SHARA] We were told the
Dwarves were a violent bunch.
Wily savages with
beards like a pelts.
Ever eating and drinking.
Ever fighting and
seldom prone to bathe.
Their arms can crush boulders
to powder, and rule a forge.
Their legs pummel the
earth as they walk.
And their axes cleave
the enemy in twain.
When day is done,
they carouse and sing as though
that night was their last.
[gasps]
[ELF C] All the other
bunkhouses are like this one.
Filled to the brim
with dying captives.
[gasps]
Even after we Elves
surrendered to the Orte,
the Dwarves kept
resisting their invasion.
Now we see the fate of
those who refused to bend.
Life as a slave in
the mines or the forge.
It sounds like our captors
have met a messy end.
I didn't think Elves
had the stones.
Ironic, don't you think?
That you of all people would
come to rescue us.
We were in a bad way.
But they came to our aid.
The Drifters.
I don't care who did it.
Just that they did.
Please let us out of here!
[DWARF CHIEF]
I beg of you! Free us!
I know... you Elves think we're
little better than beasts,
but we'll give 'em hell.
Even weakened as we are!
[TOYOHISA]
All right, then!
[DWARF CHIEF]
Huh?
I've heard much of you Dwarves.
Your beard is incredible.
You're shorter than expected.
Thought you'd be stockier, too.
Tell me true.
Are you one of those
Drifters they speak of?
That's what they call me.
But I don't give a damn about
distinctions like that.
An army marches
on its stomach!
With that in mind, let's eat!
[NOBUNAGA]
Hm? Status report, woman!
Make it quick! What's going on?
Hey! Do ya hear me?!
[OLMINU]
I can hear you.
It's just that I
don't quite know
how to describe what's
taking place here.
We freed the Dwarves,
but they're all so malnourished
that Toyoisa decided
a meal was the first
order of business.
[NOBUNAGA] Wait. You mean
to say they're eating now?
With the keep still undefeated?
[OLMINU] They raided the
larders, dragged it all here,
then threw it into
giant pots willy-nilly,
and set each one to
cook on an open fire.
[groans]
[NOBUNAGA] They're settling down
for dinner as our enemies watch?
[OLMINU yelps]
There's been a development, sir!
They're butchering
every horse in sight
and tossing them
into the pots as well!
Toyohisa!
[NOBUNAGA]
Ugh... Here's a thought.
Feed 'em after the fight!
Good news! I found
more raspberries.
Well done, Marcus.
As a reward, I grant
you the land of Gaul.
[NOBUNAGA gasps]
Make rice porridge!
[OLMINU]
Huh?
Use plenty of
water when you do!
Solid food can kill
a starving person!
Starving people overeat
and then drop dead.
The Monkey's ruthlessness
taught me that.
Uh, "the Monkey?"
[NOBUNAGA] We can't let
those Dwarves die on us.
Don't question me, Swole-mine!
Just tell them to eat slowly!
That'll have to do!
Ranmaru! Get me
some rice porridge!
Ranmaru isn't here!
Remember, dummy?!
I know that!
You don't have to correct
every little thing I say!
Agh! I miss rice!
So what is a "rice"?
And what is a "Ranmaru"?
[ORTE SOLDIER I] The Long-Ears,
they seem to 've calmed down.
What's with the smoke?
They're up to something.
[TOYOHISA]
Hey, you!
[ORTE SOLDIERS gasp]
Every Dwarf in town
has been freed!
They're having a
much needed meal,
but if you're not gone
by the time they finish,
your lives are forfeit!
We won't give chase
if you run away!
Drop your weapons and abandon
the fight, or die here!
They've gone mad with quelling
their hunger right now,
and their plates will
be bare any minute.
The horses didn't
last very long at all.
And there's even less meat on
your bones, beneath that armor!
[YOICHI] Goodness.
How pale they've all gone.
Toyohisa is playing at their
fears like a drum.
That was the last of it!
Will you surrender and live,
or fight and die?
[ORTE SOLDIERS yelp]
So what... what do we do?
They might slaughter
us either way!
Honestly, Captain!
How much time do we have
before the reinforcements
arrive and save us?
How the hell am I
supposed to know?
Please, sir. Those Dwarves
are gonna come for us.
They want revenge.
They'll dig under the stonework.
And once they're in,
our lives aren't worth a damn!
[ORTE CAPTAIN B]
Swear it, Drifter!
Swear that you'll keep your
word and let us live!
Do that, and we'll quit
the castle without delay!
Lay down your
sword at my feet
and you have nothing
to fear from me!
[TOYOHISA]
Hm. That's all of them.
Now tell me, which of
you is the commander?
[ORTE CAPTAIN B]
I am in charge!
I took your offer.
I have nothing to fear,
you told me.
You don't. I'm going to
let you disembowel yourself
with all due pomp and ceremony.
We'll prepare a spot at once.
[ORTE CAPTAIN B]
Do what?!
[TOYOHISA] I'll even be the one
to behead you at the end.
Behead?! And disembowel?!
But why?!
[TOYOHISA] You're leader
of the losing side.
There's no way you can live with
that stain upon your honor.
You will slit your belly
and die manfully.
It's your duty!
What the hell are you
talking about? This is madness!
You want me to spill my own
innards because I lost a battle?
[gasps]
So be it.
If you lack the courage to
die well, you must die poorly!
[ORTE CAPTAIN B screams]
The head of a coward
will have to suffice.
[ORTE SOLDIERS gasp]
[TOYOHISA]
Not worth the arrows, Yoichi.
[gasps]
Heh. You knew, huh?
Well, you said you
would assist me.
I knew what that meant.
Old habits are hard to break.
I was ordered to do that,
once upon a time.
[TOYOHISA]
You don't take orders anymore.
Know this. We fight as equals.
[TOYOHISA] Come on.
Let's get back to the feast.
Are we to chase the soldiers?
[YOICHI] You don't have to
do that. For now, at least.
We've earned our supper.
[dragons roar]
[OCTOBRIST A]
We're as close as we dare go.
Those dragon cavalry are adorned
with detection charms.
[DOUG]
We can't use any magic, then.
Damn the luck.
This is a difficult task.
One I'd attempt only
for you Octobrists.
If the Adventurer's
Guild had asked,
I'd have told them
to keep their coin.
[OCTOBRIST B]
You have our thanks, Doug.
[gasps]
[DOUG]
What a curious spyglass.
One of your otherworldly
relics, I assume?
Over there!
Uh? The Bronze Dragon?
What the hell?
Even the least of the six Great
Dragons is a dire threat.
Does he mean to join
the Black King's ranks?
I wonder if they halted
their southern advancement
to await him?
[OCTOBRIST A]
No. I don't think so.
Train these on the
far corner of the wall.
I think you'll have your answer.
[DOUG gasps]
[DOUG] That can't be
what it looks like!
I'm seeing it, but I
still don't believe it!
The soil. They're tilling it.
As though they intend to farm.
Who taught them to
do such a thing?
Farming is the keystone
of civilized races.
So what could the Black
King hope to accomplish,
teaching his brutes how
to grow their own rations?
The Grand Master
was right about him.
The Black King is unique
among his brethren.
He doesn't crave the
destruction of our world at all.
Merely our destruction.
That he may serve as
savior to what follows!
[MALE VOICE chants]