[TOYOHISA grunts]
I was wrong to speak of mercy.
All the men within
this fortress...
...are a disease!
[TOYOHISA] I will carve them up,
spill their foul blood,
and reduce their villainy to
so much steaming meat!
[NOBUNAGA] Give their papers
a good looking-through,
especially the maps.
We're taking everything
that might be of use.
Down to the least little scrap.
[gasps]
Never let it be
said that you sack
defeated castles
with a lack of zeal.
Well! Jiggle-Dream.
There you are!
I don't even have the
energy to respond to that.
If you don't give me grief
for it, I get to call it a win.
[OLMINU growls]
[NOBUNAGA sighs] Anyway...
Tell me, who is this man?
He's clearly important.
[OLMINU] That portrait before
you is of their leader.
He's the Father and
Founder of the Orte Empire.
He appeared out of
nowhere 60 years ago.
Whether with the Drifters or
the Ends, no one can say.
What we do know is that he
showed up at a tavern one day,
shouting about the overthrow
of the current government.
His vitriol must've struck home.
He gathered an army of those
buoyed by his words,
and marched on the capital.
A powerful orator, he played
on the people's fears,
and was catapulted into power.
Oddly enough,
after founding Orte,
he died by his own hand.
No one ever found out
what drove him to the act.
If he did come
from your world,
you don't happen to
know him, do you?
[NOBUNAGA]
Never met him.
That mustache. It's dreadful.
Nobunaga, sir!
Yes, what is it?
Toyohisa dragged the
soldiers to the courtyard.
Something about them
having a disease?
[NOBUNAGA gasps]
Wait. What the hell?
I guess I shouldn't
be surprised by this.
Of course you'd
avenge this outrage.
[ELF 6A] Milord,
what disease do they have?
[NOBUNAGA]
Still drawing breath.
[ELVES]
Huh?
[NOBUNAGA] The Elves
are a comely people.
You can tell that
just from their men.
Orte's been kidnapping
their women for a while now.
Of course their
virtue's been sullied.
Come, lad, you didn't presume
this outcome from the start?
You should not be the one
to vent your rage
upon these mongrels.
Butchery like this is meant
for a practiced hand!
Let your blood boil in
righteous indignation.
But when the moment
calls for true darkness,
leave it to the Demon King.
After all, such things
are my forte.
[ORTE SOLDIERS whimpering]
[ORTE SOLDIER A]
Please! Let us go!
Please, I don't
wanna die. Spare me!
[TOYOHISA growls]
[FEMALE ELVES whimper]
Are you all right?
[grunts]
Don't you know what
awaits you if you do this?
If the other lords
learn of this,
you'll be slaughtered to a man!
Toyohisa! Give us
the order! Do it!
Their blood must be shed!
Let us kill them!
Please!
Ki--
[exhales]
[ORTE SOLDIERS]
Huh?
[ELVES gasp]
[NOBUNAGA] Go ahead.
Kill every one of them.
All this time, you've plied
your lust upon their women.
And now that you face
a proper vengeance,
you think you might dodge it
by tossing down your arms?
Cowards.
You should have erased the
Elves when you had the chance,
for now they will
surely erase you.
Now die.
Die that I might coax
gunpowder from your flesh.
[gasps]
[NOBUNAGA]
Take aim!
[ORTE SOLDIER B shouts]
Mercy! I beg of you!
I don't want to die!
Mercy, you say?
Where was your "mercy" during
all our years of torment?!
If you were a man, you'd take
your death in silence!
[MILLS] I-I've only been at
this castle for a short while!
Your wives!
I've never touched them!
Not like this. Oh, God!
[ORTE SOLDIERS whimper]
Send them to hell!
[ORTE SOLDIERS grunt]
[gasps]
[TOYOHISA groans]
[NOBUNAGA]
Look who's awake already!
I thought you'd be drooling
down there for longer.
You boys from the
boonies have thick skulls!
We were busy while
you slumbered.
Quite the bloody tableau.
And dirtier work than I wanted
you to sully your hands with.
There's honorable killing
and what I oversaw here.
What's another
stain to the karma
for an old butcher like me?
[laughs]
Ise-Nagashima, The Azai
and Asakura clans,
Enryaku Monastery,
up on Mt. Hiei.
Thousands of them--
[grunts]
Who gives a damn how
many you've cut down?
Don't try to spare me!
I'm a warrior, the same as you!
[gasps]
[whimpers]
[YOICHI]
We're back, Milord.
You two seem to be locked
in a quarrel. Are you...?
No quarreling here, Yoichi.
He's right, this time.
Is he now? My mistake.
[NOBUNAGA] Nobody's bowled
me over in anger like that
since my father.
There's a comfort in it.
Aye. My tutor and
my father both.
And then, suddenly,
I'd grown older than my father
had ever been.
[MILLS whimpers]
[whimpering continues]
This one needs an arrow.
No, I don't! I've done nothing!
I swear it! I've never lain
with a woman in my life!
There's no bravery in this man,
but I think he speaks the truth.
We were loath to kill him for
the crime of simply being here.
My word. How merciful.
[NOBUNAGA]
Too pure to be killed, eh?
Octo-Breast!
Be a dear and let
him grope you!
You be a dear and die!
I'll take the heads and pay
them their due respect.
Their souls are freed
from this villainy.
Their bodies will be saltpeter!
[OLMINU]
Rumors of the Drifters' heroism
spread through the surrounding
villages like wildfire.
Could these outlanders
have truly liberated
an Elven village and defeated
the local magistrate?
But soon, as the
newly-freed Elf-wives
hurried back to their villages,
and the loving arms
of their menfolk,
the veracity of these rumors
could no longer be in any doubt.
Of course, as befit
the wily strategist,
Nobunaga saw that
none of the women
sped home empty-handed.
They bore a message.
It was a masterstroke.
Calling thee Elves to action.
Appealing to their emotions
and their logic
in equal measure.
"Your women have returned home,
but for how long?
When the lord's
replacement is named,
will you meekly hand them back,
so that he may slake his lust?
Or will you fight?
For your families!
For your homes!
Join us, and I will see
that you keep them!"
He sent another missive proving
that decades of conquest
had left Orte stretched thin,
based on facts Nobunaga gleaned
from the defeated lord's papers.
He's a pervert, yes,
but a brilliant one.
Emboldened by his words,
the Elf villages rose in revolt.
Little by little, the Elves
are throwing off the yoke
of 40 years of Orte oppression.
[footsteps]
[grunting]
[music plays]
[EASY sighs]
[chuckles]
[gasps]
[growls]
[EASY]
What the hell is going on?!
This is bullshit, Murasaki,
and you know it!
Day and night,
every time I turn around,
you troll me
with those Drifters!
[music crescendos]
[SAINT-GERMI]
We're losing on the eastern
and western front alike.
The situation in the
far north is vexing,
and the Elves are feeling
their proverbial oats.
Hate to say it,
but this empire's living
on borrowed time.
[ARISTOCRAT A]
This war will be the ruin of us.
We lack the manpower
to keep this up.
Forty years of non-stop
conflict has bled us dry.
We've had to resort
to levying troops
from the hinterlands as of late.
We're also running
low on materiel.
Tax revenue, seized assets
and plunder have all
slowed to a trickle!
The time may have
come for a ceasefire.
[ARISTOCRAT B]
Surely you jest!
The Father intended Orte
to last for a millennium.
Our kingdom is built
upon that truth!
Without conquest,
Orte cannot endure!
A conundrum.
[SAINT-GERMI]
Oh, the gang's all here!
And I'm just waltzing in late,
scoundrel that I am.
Can you find it in your hearts
to forgive me? Much obliged.
Ah. Count San-Germain, welcome.
[ARISTOCRATS]
Hm?
I had hoped with all
my heart to be on time,
but unexpected business
demanded my attention.
Why do they tolerate
this mincing popinjay?
Shh! Keep it to yourself!
He's been the ruin
of men for far less.
That's Count San-Germain.
Huh? Him? You're kidding me!
[GUARD B]
That "mincing popinjay"
rules over a quarter
of the empire.
When the Father led his coup,
he was the first noble
to heed the call.
[gulps]
[GUARD B] Without that
historic act of betrayal,
the Orte Empire would have
been done before it began.
Since that day, the Count's
acted with impunity.
He's never taken up arms in war.
He lives a life of ease.
Wait, you just said
he helped the Father.
That was 50 years ago!
I know.
How wizened of a man hides
beneath that make-up?
[SAINT-GERMI] Hm. I've brought
an interesting titbit
of information along with me.
Consider it my 'mea culpa'.
You're all aware of the fleet
that keeps our troops in the
west well-provisioned, yes?
[gasps] Anyone have a writing
implement I could borrow?
Give me something
to write with. Quickly!
I'd be honored to sacrifice
my lipstick to the cause,
my dear contessa!
Use mine, or the heartbreak
will surely kill me!
[SAINT-GERMI] Shut
up! Just give it to me!
If memory serves,
I asked you many a time
as to whether this sea-route...
was a sensible option.
[ARISTOCRATS]
Hm?
Now, the destruction of our
fleet has proven my point.
What?
But how?
[ORTE SOLDIER A]
Another direct hit!
[ORTE SOLDIER B] Damn it!
They're taking on water!
[ORTE SOLDIER C grunts] They're
swarming them like vultures!
[ORTE SOLDIER B] How many
of our ships are left?
[ORTE SOLDIER A]
Incoming gryphon!
Damn those greedy bastards!
That merchant guild
will be the end of us all!
Concocted by the
Shylock Company,
and delivered by
the Gu Binnen Guild!
I hope our cargo satisfies!
[ORTE SOLDIERS yell]
Tell me, you Orte clods!
How do you like our
highly-explosive recipe
of fish oil and animal fat, huh?
Eat your fill,
you sons of bitches!
Take some to that bristle-lipped
Father of yours in hell!
Tora! Tora! Tora!
[PILOT A]
Commander, a question!
What is the meaning
of your battle-cry?
[COMMANDER] Huh? Just something
I picked up from the Admiral.
[chuckles]
You're supposed to yell it
when the enemy
never saw ya coming!
[PILOT A chuckles]
Tora! Tora! Tora!
[COMMANDER]
Maybe... we win this time.
This is come-uppance
for all the chaos we've
sown amid our neighbors.
That said, making a foe
of the Merchant Guild
of all people was a
particularly fatal gambit.
[SAINT-GERMI laughs]
Can't say I didn't warn you!
Our prospects on
land are no better.
The Elves have
decided to fight for
their freedom after
all these years.
Do pardon my maiden blush.
They leave me weak in the knees!
The serfs lash out
from time to time!
Nothing our troops can't quash!
The more pressing issue...
[SAINT-GERMI] They've proven
me right. Morons, one and all.
Orte increased its
holdings through conquest,
its borders ever expanding.
That means the Elves
rising up in rebellion's the
mere tip of the iceberg.
The other conquered races
will find courage in
their seditious example.
Whispers of freedom
will whip through the
territories like wildfire,
igniting a
full-blown revolution.
Our satellite
states to the west
shall prove fertile
ground for these ideas.
When they rise up, we'll be
cut off from the lion's
share of our fighting men.
And with that the
empire is in checkmate!
[laughs]
I think my nose could use
a thorough powdering!
I hope you'll excuse me!
Best of luck with
the upcoming carnage!
I bid you all a fond farewell!
Dear contessa,
you seem nervous.
[SAINT-GERMI] We're leaving
here with all due haste!
Oh! Be a love and grab
that painting, would you?
Ah! The candelabra!
Contact the leaders of the
Elven rebellion immediately.
Wait, I heard that Drifters
might be mixed up in this.
I'll initiate the parley myself.
[ALLISTER] Elves?! I want
to go see the Elves, too!
[FULAME] No fair! If you
take him, you have to take me!
Silence!
[SHARA]
Halt!
[ELVES gasp]
[gasp] You're all from
Fizona Village, aren't you!
So glad you came!
Shara, right? I read that
message you sent along.
If we don't do it now,
we never will.
More and more Elves are
throwing in with us, friend.
We can win this!
You wrote that Drifters
spearheaded this whole thing.
What're they like?
I'm not entirely
sure how to answer.
They're... like no one I've met!
Even though they aided
you in your moment of need,
they are not of our blood.
How do they differ from
the other Short-Ears?
Are they worthy of trust?
They are to me.
I trust them with my life.
[TOYOHISA] Don't tell
me you're still upset.
You really should
calm down, milord.
This fit of pique is unseemly.
You were a leader of men!
[TOYOHISA] I still don't
see why you're so angry
in the first place.
What kind of fool are you?!
Why are you giving the village
heads a spot at the table?
I could have sculpted
you into an warlord!
You could have
become king, Toyohisa!
[TOYOHISA] Nuance was
never a strength of mine.
When I see a problem, I run
toward it and cut it in half.
Nobunaga.
You can see through a man's
machinations at a glance,
but the strings that
move his heart to action
remain unknown to you, even now.
Huh?
[TOYOHISA] I know the Elves
will follow me into war.
And I could name myself king.
Until the day they let
fly their arrows at us.
They know nothing of
Honno-ji Temple here.
But someday they'll recreate it.
Do you wish to suffer
that twice? I do not!
The cost is too high.
You don't think I can
read people's emotions?
Gotta say, that's just
downright insulting.
I've faced so much betrayal
I know what's in
there sight unseen.
Were you stabbed in the
back that many times?
Lemme see.
Twice by my brother Nobukatsu.
Twice each by the
Katsuie and Hayashi.
Azai, Matsunaga, Araki, Hatano,
Bessho, Mitsuhide.
Yeah, that's a lot!
[NOBUNAGA]
Know this;
Once my mind is made up,
I never relent.
I will make you a king.
[ELVES chattering]
What is he trying
to accomplish?
Having them bring the
contents of their latrines.
[OLMINU]
No idea.
[chuckles] If you don't
want to get blown to bits,
pour with caution.
Hey, Shara.
We're going to need
a lot more of this.
Tell the villagers to dig up as
much as they can and bring it
to me without delay.
Are all Drifters this
obsessed with shit?
Pardon, sir.
[NOBUNAGA]
Hm?
[SHARA] I asked our
blacksmiths as you bade me.
But as I feared, they said
copying this was beyond them.
[NOBUNAGA]
So that's the verdict, huh?
I should've given
the craftsmen of Sakai
and Kunitomo more credit.
Who can do the job?
[SHARA] Perhaps the Dwarves
would be up to the task.
Their knack for metal-work
is their one saving grace.
Whatever they are, they'll do.
[YOICHI]
All right!
I'm here to sharpen your archery
skills to a razor's edge!
I am Nasu Suketaka Yoichi!
Rrgh! And I own you now!
I am going to subject you
to training of such intensity,
every arrow you shoot will
be a part of your soul!
After every answer you give me,
you'll shout, "Minamoto banzai"!
[laughs]
"Minamoto"?
Just do it.
[YOICHI] Where 100 shots out of
100 may have sufficed before,
now you must make
10,000 out of 100!
Prepare yourselves!
[ELVES]
No way, Minamoto banzai.
While jesting,
his face gets very odd
but when he's serious,
he's a sigh to behold.
He is too beautiful
to be a Short-Ear.
I'm not sure what led you to
that conclusion, my dear Elves.
I was the youngest of 11
brothers within the Nasu clan.
And my looks were the
most unfortunate by far.
No words could do
their beauty justice!
Where they would tread,
flowers bloomed anew.
Oceans cleared a path.
And gold fell from the sky!
You do believe my words,
don't you?
[TOYOHISA shouts]
[ELVES gasp]
[TOYOHISA] That's how we're
taught back in Satsuma.
To put all of your strength
and heart into one slash,
the result be damned.
It's impressive...
...but if the blade should fail
to connect with your opponent,
then what?
He strikes you dead.
Your spirit leaves
this realm, honor intact.
[TOYOHISA] The Elves are
useless with a sword in hand.
I don't think they're
meant for such things.
[NOBUNAGA]
Hm...
[YOICHI] They make up
for it with a bow.
Their skill at archery
is beyond reproach.
Wish their blacksmiths
were as trusty.
[YOICHI grunts]
Why do I feel such icy dread?
[OLMINU]
Huh?
Something approaches.
And it's not the rank-and-file
of the Orte Army.
They are coming for us.
[gasps]
[TOYOHISA] The night air
smells of Sekigahara.
Of blood, waiting to be spilt!
[MALE VOICE chants]
[BLACK KING] Find them!
Hunt them down!
[JOAN OF ARC] En avant,
Gilles de Rais!
That righteous stench will lead
us straight to the Drifters!
[BLACK KING]
End them!
Cast them down
into the darkness!
Before these
branches bear fruit,
consign them to the flames.
[MALE VOICE chants]