[EASY laughs] So what if
you brought them over?
Your stupid little Drifters.
All you're doing is tossing
'em into a meat-grinder.
They don't stand a snowball's
chance in hell against my Ends.
You know in your heart
I'm gonna win this thing.
All you're doing is
running down the clock.
Admit defeat like the bland
bureaucrat you are, Murasaki!
[gasps]
[EASY]
You son of a bitch!
[OLMINU]
You're not the only ones.
People like you, who were
brought here from your world.
People of singular skill,
are known in this
world as Drifters.
But others have been brought
here from your realm, too.
Those given over to darkness.
They delight in death.
We call them, the Ends.
As sworn members of the
Octobrist Organization,
it's our job to evaluate
Drifters like you,
so that we may unite
them against the Ends,
and safeguard our world.
So, uh, wanna untie me now?
Not a chance!
That was just gibberish
falling outta your mouth.
--[OLMINU grunts]
--[NOBUNAGA laughs]
If you think I'm a Drifter,
you're mistaken.
But you're equally wrong
if you think I'm an End.
Yes!
Behold the Demon King of the
Sixth Heaven in all his glory!
Your "good" and "evil"?
These words are nothing
to one such as I!
[grunts] I exist beyond
your petty judgment!
[TOYOHISA] Look at you,
bellowing like a kabuki actor.
Have you no shame?
Not really.
Course not.
The way you carry on,
why should I
expect any subtlety?
So. Why do you think
that we're Drifters?
Because, I can't imagine
you joining the other side.
[chuckles]
How so?
[OLMINU]
Those brought here as Ends
have cast aside their
former humanity.
They hate humanity now.
They want no part of it.
They look at their fellow man
as something worthless.
A blight, a spreading cancer.
I don't know what could have
happened to them in your world
to inspire such rage.
But now they burn with it.
The rage fuels and
sustains them.
It's turned each of them
into something less,
and something more.
Every thought and deed
in service of one goal,
The slaughter of all mankind.
They first gathered
in the north,
bending the monsters
to their dark will,
before leading an army
of them into our land.
If we don't stop them,
they will destroy everything
good and pure in the world.
That's why I beg of you.
Please help us. We can't
win this fight alone!
So how robust is your army?
Army?
[NOBUNAGA] I don't give a
damn if they're monsters or men.
What's clear is,
your foe has troops.
You Octobrists must have some
kind of standing army in place.
W-Well? We, uh... That is...
"As sworn members
of the Octobrists,
it's our job to evaluate
Drifters like--!"
[NOBUNAGA]
So nothing?
[OLMINU] Uh... We put
out the call for troops
to various kings
and feudal lords
and then we'll assign Drifters
to command those forces.
You are such an idiot!
[OLMINU whimpers]
[NOBUNAGA] I don't know the
particulars of your world yet,
but I know this much;
A lord holds the reins
to his soldiers.
That's what makes him
lord in the first place.
No ruler will ever
cede control of his men.
Especially not to
some untested outsider!
It doesn't matter
how terrifying
these Ends of yours may
be out on the battlefield.
A king is gonna value his
pride over his own head.
Even as his foes pour
into his last stronghold,
a leader will keep his
troops on a tight leash,
'til it's time to
slit his own belly.
You should know that, idiot.
A lord's a lord most anywhere.
People are ruled by emotion,
whether they live
in a palace or a hut.
I'm an avid student of
the human condition.
Almost won me Japan.
[TOYOHISA] This old trickster.
Is he the real Oda Nobunaga?
Or just a deluded fool
who wishes it were so?
[OLMINU]
Then what're we to do?
Only Drifters have any
chance of winning.
But you'd need an
army at your back!
[NOBUNAGA] The answer
is staring you in the face.
We Drifters will overthrow
all of your feudal lords!
[gasps]
From this point on,
Toyohisa will lead us on a
mission of utter conquest.
[TOYOHISA]
Huh?
And you will support us.
Help us topple your empire
for the sake of this world!
This is no time for
half-measures, woman!
You must be bold!
Wait a damn second! Why am I
suddenly in charge of all this?
[YOICHI]
Huh?
Don't you remember taking the
leader's spot the other day?
[NOBUNAGA]
Bet you're beat!
Please, make yourself comfy
on this nearby wooden crate!
[growls]
Of course there was an angle!
You have met Oda, right?
You're not much of
a tactician, are ya, kid?
[TOYOHISA]
Why I oughtta!
[ALL shouting]
[OLMINU sighs] Grand Master,
these Drifters are insane.
The way they're behaving;
it's simply barbaric!
[OLMINU] That said, their idea
does have a certain appeal.
[OLMINU] Unfortunately,
we've suffered many
an attack by the Ends before.
[OLMINU]
And every time,
the death and destruction they
wrought were overwhelming.
But now the carnage is absolute.
Half-measures are useless!
They mean to slay
every one of us!
[OLMINU] All by decree
of their Black King!
[RASPUTIN] My Dark Majesty.
The Northern Wall of Carneades
has been reduced to
so much broken stone.
[BLACK KING]
What of our losses, Rasputin?
I would know of them.
[RASPUTIN]
Two hundred seventy-four dead
from the Goblin special forces.
345 from the Kobold
advanced guard and
four dragons shot down.
Our losses were by
no means substantial,
but the dragons will
be hard to replace.
[BLACK KING] Bring me
to those who need succor.
Do you mean... to aid them?
[BLACK KING]
With all of my heart.
Goblins, Kobolds, and Dragons
each have served me faithfully.
I will save whom I can,
for they are my brethren.
You are mercy incarnate,
Your Highness.
[GOBLINS growling, snorting]
[speaking Orte]
[grunts]
[gasps]
[GOBLIN C sighs, speaks Orte]
[grunting, gasping]
[BLACK KING]
My brethren,
you took on these wounds
in my name. Come forth.
[BLACK KING] Send word
to all who would listen.
The Northern Wall is no more.
There are many who believe
the humans to be unbeatable.
A force eternal. This will
gladden their hearts
and they will
bolster our ranks.
[BLACK KING]
Once, I loved mankind.
But they, they forsook me.
And now, I bless
the baser creatures
and seek the end of humanity.
[RASPUTIN] They were
fools to deny you, Milord.
[BLACK KING] The Drifters who
fled here tonight yet live.
[MALE VOICE chants]
[BLACK KING]
Search... Search.
Discover where those vile
magicians have hidden them away.
And where they mean
to smuggle them next.
Don't let them meet
as a force united.
Though you hate the
whole of mankind,
let none distract you
from your quarry.
The Drifters are thine
mortal foe. Give chase.
Hunt them down. Kill them.
I suppose I should pick a side!
[chuckles] Whoever catches
my fancy, I guess.
[BLACK KING] I am relentless.
The Inexorable Tribulation
who wanders the land,
proclaiming his wrath.
My crusade against
mankind is righteous
and I am nothing if not patient.
I will take up the sword
until every last human
lies slaughtered
and every demi-human tastes
of the salvation that
man has squandered.
[BLACK KING]
Such is my will!
Don't you dare die on me,
you broken-ass piece of shit!
[NAOSHI grunting]
Lift your nose!
Lift your fucking nose!
[NAOSHI] That hurt
like a son-of-a-bitch!
[grunts]
[NAOSHI gasps]
[growling]
The hell are you looking at?
Who wants to get their
skull caved in first?
[ELF 4 speaking Orte]
[speaking Orte]
[ELVES sigh]
[SHARA speaking Orte]
[ELF E speaking Orte]
[speaking Orte]
Uh... What is he doing?
Damn it! They don't
understand him at all.
Hey! Hey, you!
Tell me, dammit!
Ask me something!
How the hell can you
speak our language?
There's a perfectly
reasonable explanation!
We're a bunch of magicians,
and we've been keeping track of
every little thing
you say and do!
But really it's because
the Grand Master
created this instant
translation charm.
Aren't you impressed?
Instant fluency at the
tip of your fingers.
Our master's genius
is undeniable!
[YOICHI grunts]
So I could have used
one of those all along?
Hey! No fair! The lad's been
tying himself in knots
trying learn their
language the right way!
How was I s'posed to know that?
[NOBUNAGA] Apologize for
crushing his spirit!
[OLMINU]
I-It was an accident!
[NOBUNAGA] Just tell him
you're sorry, woman!
Look at the poor little scamp!
[OLMINU]
All right!
I'm sorry I told you about
the charms, okay?
[NOBUNAGA]
That's better. Now gimme one!
[OLMINU] Uh sure. Lemme just dig
through these for a second.
For someone from
your place n' time.
I know it's here. Isn't it?
Oh, this is embarrassing.
[YOICHI grunts]
[ELVES gasp]
[YOICHI]
Good evening, all.
Good evening, all...
Idiot! They were scared
enough of us as it was!
Don't slap it onto his face!
Sorry about that!
I was just so glad to
find the right charm!
[NOBUNAGA]
Looks like the handiwork
of an onmyoji from Kyoto.
I'd like to meet this "Grand
Master" of hers for myself.
'Ey Boob Girl, forgot your name.
It's Olmine! Not that difficult.
[NOBUNAGA] Give me the
history of these Long Ears.
What? The whole thing?
However this became their lot
in life. Tell me that part.
[OLMINU]
Yes, sir. These are Elves.
Their problems
began many years ago,
when the humans attacked them.
Their attackers would
come out victorious, sadly.
The Elves've lived as
their serfs ever since.
Right. And how would
you characterize them?
[OLMINU] Well, they're very
long-lived. And they're proud.
Or used to be, at least,
before it came to this.
[chuckling]
That's more'n enough
to work with!
[laughs]
Let's begin.
[TOYOHISA]
hm?
[NOBUNAGA] Face them
and say what I tell you.
Better if you do it.
They've seen you
take a few heads.
[OLMINU]
Uh?
So here's the plan.
Tell 'em all that stuff we
talked about before.
Just lay it on thick.
Hit 'em with the hard sell.
[TOYOHISA grunts]
You know why you got betrayed
at Honnoji Temple, right?
'Cause of crap like this!
Shut up! Tell 'em!
[ELVES gasp]
[TOYOHISA]
All right. Listen up, you!
If your forefathers were alive,
they'd be ashamed!
[ELVES gasp]
[TOYOHISA] Your children feel
the humiliation!
How could they not?
Don't you wish to
live as a free people?
Will you die on
your knees a slave?
Or will you die on your feet?
And redeem your legacy?
[gasps]
Decide!
[ELVES gasp]
Of... of course we've
shamed our forefathers!
We know they've got
us under their heel!
We would give
anything to live free!
Well said.
Follow me. Time to
cast off your chains!
[ELVES mutter]
[NOBUNAGA]
Look at this!
Such piss and
vinegar in his soul.
It kind of reminds me
of another young man.
Hey! Why did you
make me Commander?
You've been waging war a hell
of a lot longer, old man!
[NOBUNAGA laughs]
I much prefer the role of
puppet-master in the shadows!
[laughs]
Don't act like I'm your son.
[gasps]
He died at Nijou
Palace years ago!
Struck down by Mitsuhide!
I'm Shimazu Toyohisa,
not Oda Nobutada, dammit!
[OLMINU]
Eh...
[NOBUNAGA grunts]
How stupid do you think I am?
I know you're not my son,
you mouthy bastard!
What, I miss him so
much I see him in you?
Don't flatter yourself, boy!
Tch. You fool.
[NOBUNAGA]
Heh. You damn fool.
[TOYOHISA]
I may have gone too far.
If my father were still alive,
he'd be around that same age.
Look at you. Pining for
your old man, right?
Don't forget, Iehisa is dead.
And I, am Oda Nobunaga!
Satsuma? Where the hell is that?
[growls]
[grunting]
[TOYOHISA] What the hell did
you just say, you jackass?
[NOBUNAGA] You heard me!
Whatcha gonna do about it?
[ELF A]
I thought they were allies,
but they started fighting!
[ELF B] Someone break
them up! Quickly!
[ELVES shouting]
[sighs]
This brings back memories
of how we used to fight.
Well met, Brother!
The ten of us have pledged
fealty to the Taira clan!
ou're with the Genji, right?
Great! Then it's brother
against brother!
[YOICHI BROTHERS]
Fight us! Fight us!
[YOICHI] Ten of them
against me by my lonesome.
What fun we had!
I would do it again in a second.
[YOICHI shouts]
What the hell was that for?!
[YOICHI laughs]
You're an archer, jackass!
[SHARA grunts]
That's quite enough!
[ALL]
Hm?
Whatever your quarrel may be,
this is no time for fighting
amongst one another!
The lord's men could
be approaching!
What's your name?
I am the son of the
village elder they killed.
I'm Shara. You saved
my brothers' lives.
Ah! So he's your big brother?
[BOTH]
Mm-hm!
[NOBUNAGA
"Could be approaching"?
Don't make me laugh.
Of course they're coming.
No doubt about it.
Not a-one of those soldiers
made it out of here alive.
Only question is how long it'll
take to muster reinforcements.
I think four days
would prove sufficient.
Too long.
The dead were well-armed.
Gear's no issue.
Closer to three.
My clan could have
done it in one.
That's because you had
nothing better to do!
Living out in the damn sticks!
Point being, the sunrise
after the next,
will be the last
this village sees.
Then help us! Or we're doomed!
Lend us your strength,
that we may survive!
My people are unschooled
in the ways of combat!
Forty years ago,
when our land was
conquered by the cruel Orte,
we were but children.
Our men who could fight
all died in the futile
quest to defend us.
When it comes to warfare,
we are worse than useless!
I ask--no--I beg you!
[NOBUNAGA, YOICHI, TOYOHISA]
Heh?
Tsh. I'm still hung up
on one of the details.
You, with the ears!
How old're you?
Uh... only 106.
[BOTH gasp]
Don't lie to me, elf.
I've killed men for
less back in my homeland.
I'm telling the truth.
Okay. How old're you two, then?
I'm 39.
I'm 36.
[ALL gasp]
[NOBUNAGA]
Boobine! How can this be true?
It's Olmine!
You're never gonna
remember my name, are you?!
And who said you could honk
my boob with wild abandon?!
The Elves are blessed
with great longevity.
Five to six times greater
than yours or mine.
So they mature
more slowly overall.
What's the matter?
Yeah, what's wrong?
I'm younger'n them!
Years ago, this was part
of the Elves' own country.
Before a human
kingdom conquered it.
Orte.
Orte defeated their Dwarven
and Halfling neighbors in
a similar fashion.
Forcing those once-free people
to toil to the kingdom's benefit
in the fields and mines.
From then on, Orte's fancied
itself an empire,
championing human
supremacy with an iron fist.
Is it still expanding,
this "Orte Empire?"
[OLMINU] They're waging
numerous battles.
Locked in perpetual combat
to retain their holdings.
[NOBUNAGA]
Much as I'd expect.
Hanging onto one's
spoils is the real pisser.
You have only two choices
once you've taken a place.
Either you destroy it entirely,
or attend to its every need,
like a doting paramour.
[OLMINU] The Orte of
old would have been
a good ally to have at
our side during a war
with the Black King,
but much has changed.
[NOBUNAGA] Instead, the Elves
were left to nurse their grudge.
Forty years
it's festered now.
Every mother's son is filled
with the embers of rage,
and the lord's men fanned them
to full strength
with that attack.
That's why they were so quick
to skewer the knight
after a little prodding.
But the punishment will
be swift, and harsh.
More soldiers are
marching here as we speak,
with orders to leave
none of you alive.
Tell me, how will you face
this threat, Toyohisa?
You are the commander,
after all.
Come, pride of the Shimazu.
Let's see your
tactics in action.
[TOYOHISA]
We let them in.
And then we cut them down.
[hooves thumping]
[ORTE SOLDIER A]
Isn't this a bit much?
Deploying 200 soldiers to wipe
one measly Elven
village off the map?
[ORTE SOLDIER B]
If you believe the rumors,
they killed Aram's whole squad.
[ORTE SOLDIER A]
Them and what army?
[ORTE SOLDIER C] Those Long-Ears
don't have the stones to do it!
I heard it was Drifters,
not Elves, who killed 'em all.
Wait... Drifters?
[ORTE SOLDIER F] Not even
a bunch. Only a handful.
Are they really
that strong? Impossible!
[ORTE SOLDIER H]
Nothing!
There's no one
here either, Sir.
The village is empty.
What the hell is going on?
They wouldn't just leave.
This makes no sense!
[TOYOHISA] After dark,
every soldier's life is forfeit.
Every one of their
heads is coming off!
[MALE VOICE chants]