[YOICHI grunting]
[YOICHI]
That was close.
Another few moments,
and I would've...
[YOSHITSUNE] Tragic.
You've really lost your edge.
By all rights,
you should be a corpse.
No, that's impossible!
Yoshitsune. How?
[YOSHITSUNE]
What were you thinking,
fighting that beast
by your lonesome?
Little fool!
What? Did you mistake
yourself for a warrior?
Remember what you did
at the Battle of Yashima?
I certainly do.
[YOSHITSUNE chuckles]
So pathetic!
[YOICHI] Even here I'm to be
granted no peace from you?
Where are you hiding?!
Yoshitsune. Upon my life, I--
[grunts]
I will follow your
orders no longer!
[YOSHITSUNE laughs]
Do as you will, Yoichi.
Of course. He, he, he...
Next time we can
speak face-to-face.
[NOBUNAGA]
How do you fit into all this?
Clearly, you're involved.
[HARUAKIRA] I'm just a man.
A man who hates the Ends.
I'm the leader of the
Octobrist organization
to which Olmine has
pledged her allegiance.
Giving aiding to the Drifters
ranks as first among my duties.
And, the best way I
can lend them that aid
is to destroy every
End I encounter.
I believe that you're
a Drifter your own self.
What's your name?
[HARUAKIRA]
Abe no Haruakira.
"Abe no Haruakira"?
You mean Abe no Seimei?
That's one way to read
the kanji of my name.
I prefer the common version,
as it keeps me grounded.
[NOBUNAGA]
Hm...
[TOYOHISA]
Good.
[HARUAKIRA]
Huh?
[TOYOHISA] It looks like we
won our fights all around.
I'm not in the mood
for another stranger.
Who are you?
Easy! It's Abe no Seimei.
He needs no introduction.
Abe no Seimei.
In the flesh! Wild, huh?
Who now?
[grunts]
No idea?
No clue! Let it go!
I pursued matters
arcane in Kyoto.
[TOYOHISA]
A fop from the capitol, then?
Your garb is odd. Is that
what passed for fashion?
No. I did not adopt this
uniform until my arrival here.
[TOYOHISA] Just as well.
It's way too fancy for some
random back-alley
fortune-teller.
[HARUAKIRA]
Huh?
You'll have to excuse him.
Young people, right?
He'd be really
impressed if he knew.
Sir. Such sniffling
is quite unbecoming.
How will you conquer the Ends
if you can't even
conquer your own ego?
So, you were brought to this
world just as we were.
Sent hence by that
unflappable man
holding court
in that hallway.
[HARUAKIRA]
Yes. I never saw it coming.
[gasps]
[HARUAKIRA] The man.
He opened a portal somehow.
And in that moment,
my life began anew.
In time, I came to
realize my appointed task.
Instead of wasting
my time with imps,
or reading the night
sky for omens,
I was sent here to
destroy the Ends.
[NOBUNAGA]
Ah. So that hulking spearman
and the fire-witch are
called Ends, I take it?
He did not go easily!
I assume you dealt with her.
I did. Knocked her into the well
and brained her one
for good measure.
Wha--?
You didn't finish her off, then?
[HARUAKIRA]
Uh! Quickly!
[NOBUNAGA]
No woman.
Guess she got away. Must be
tougher than she looks.
[HARUAKIRA]
"Got away"?
She got away because
you didn't kill her!
That woman is an End!
They're a plague!
[TOYOHISA] Taking the head
of a woman isn't heroic.
It's shameful.
I don't care what she is!
She's a woman, but she is
an End first and foremost,
which means you have to--
I'm not your servant
to order around!
[gasps]
[TOYOHISA]
No woman dies by my hand.
Mark me well, fortune-teller!
[TOYOHISA]
He summoned us,
but we are not the man in
the hallway's playthings.
We write our own fate.
[HARUAKIRA gasps]
Our principles are nothing
you get to overrule.
[HARUAKIRA]
Such resolve.
This is the unbowed soul of a
man who's known only strife.
They are brutal, yet they
hold themselves to a code.
That may be their saving grace.
The reason they were plucked
from the multitudes.
However, the Ends must
not be suffered to live.
Whether woman or man,
prince or pauper,
villain or victim of old,
their kind must be
ushered to oblivion!
[OLMINU]
Grand Master, sir?
If I may inquire, who's the
old man in the wagon?
[HARUAKIRA]
Hannibal Barca, of Carthage.
A Drifter, like the others.
But I fear his mind has been
a clouded mirror as of late.
He's been getting worse
over the past several days.
The loss of his foe
may be the end of him.
Huh?
We had another
Drifter from his era.
Scipio, of the mighty
Roman Empire.
The two men were bitter rivals,
but there was respect there.
Scipio's presence
kept Hannibal lucid.
Suffice it to say,
the road had its perils.
We were attacked by the Black
King's troops along the way.
[DRAGON roars]
[gasps]
[shouts]
Scipio!
Shit!
[ENDS SOLDIERS shouting]
[HARUAKIRA]
Pursued by land and air alike,
there was no chance of
going back to look for him.
HQ sent out a team,
but there's been no sign
of him since he fell.
Pray he's not in the
clutches of the Black King.
Thus, Hannibal's decline.
His bladder would
betray him before,
but now his mind does as well.
For all the bile they
would spout at one another.
Scipio was important to him.
A foe who demanded
his very best.
[SCIPIO groans]
Volo redire Roma plachit!
Volo balneum! Volo balneum!
[sobs]
[SCIPIO] Since my ignominious
flight from the cart,
I've been trudging
into the unknown.
I follow this path
of flattened greenery,
hoping it leads to shelter,
but there's nothing.
I paid my dues back
during the Africa campaign!
After saving Rome itself,
don't I deserve better than
havin' to wander through
the brush like a
common foot soldier?
Gods!
This is an insult to my
service and intellect alike!
[gasps]
Quid.... Quid hoc est?
[SCIPIO]
Canis? Homo-canis?
Uh? Ah! Quid? Quid?
Manere! Manere! Ne faceris!
[NAOSHI]
What the hell am I lookin' at?
Hey, you moron!
I asked you a question!
[SCIPIO]
Huh?
[NAOSHI] If you even
breathe on my plane,
you get my boot
straight up your ass!
Huh? Some white guy?
You better not be
a fuckin' American!
Speak up, ya
blonde-haired dickbag.
But if you are an American,
I'm gonna kick your fucking ass!
Got it, asshole?
[SCIPIO] He certainly is a
belligerent one, this savage.
I can hardly believe
he's got the mind
to have flown that
odd device over
the Battle at the Wall
to such great effect.
Could it be? This bellowing
baboon is a fellow Drifter?
His words hold no meaning!
It's all'a so staccato!
From where does he hail?
And why are his eyes like that?
Look at those scribbles
that pass for writing!
But of course he
can't speak Latin,
lingua franca of
the civilized world!
His tribe must live beyond
the cartographer's ken,
the poor devil.
Still, there's no way
this howling beast
has not heard the name
of my motherland!
Roma!
Roma, huh?
Uh...
[gasps]
[BOTH chuckle]
Tandem intelligere.
[SCIPIO]
O Rome, the mere mention of you
forges bonds of
brotherhood eternal!
You assholes surrendered!
You abandoned the Axis right
when it needed you most,
you rat-bastard!
[WOLF MAN A] Well, looks like
the sky-god is angry again.
Why couldn't a friendly god have
come? This one frightens me.
You moron!
[SCIPIO]
Non barbarus!
[NAOSHI] That is it! You're
gonna apologize to Germany,
you toga-wearing asshole,
if I have to break
every bone in your body!
What is this odd cylinder?
That there's a cartridge.
"Cartridge"?
My word, we got a neophyte.
Beggin' your pardon. I done
forgot you're right ancient.
First you pack
in the gunpowder,
and top it all off
with the killin' bit.
The cartridge goes
in the chamber,
hammer hits the primer
when the trigger's pulled.
And if you're lucky,
you've let the daylight
into some murderous cuss.
[chuckles]
--[KID] What the...?
--[gunshots continue]
[KID] Don't go wastin' bullets!
You loco som'bitch!
[chuckles]
[NOBUNAGA]
And that one there?
The one that tore
the giant to pieces?
How did you manage
to fire it so fast?
That's called a Gatlin' gun.
Turn the crank,
and watch 'em fall down.
Heh. So much scrap iron,
now we're outta magazines.
[BUTCH]
Hey pardner, feelin' sickly?
[BOTH]
Huh?
[NOBUNAGA]
Ha. Glad I had already started
in on making gunpowder.
A gun like this could
change the tide
of battle like nothing
I've ever seen.
We could take down armies
of impossible size
with this clever thing.
Riflemen will abandon
their boxy formations
and attack from choke-points.
Cavalry and spearmen will
become relics of the past.
Oh! Yes! How I desire it!
No matter the price!
[HARUAKIRA]
That's no easy task.
The Octobrists have
been looking into it.
That gun would be the
jewel of our arsenal.
But we can't solve the riddle
of how to fashion them.
We have shown this
to many a blacksmith.
and all of them admit
it lies beyond their skill.
Even you, Nobunaga lived
hundreds of years
before these were possible.
And that's to say nothing
of the black powder
within the bullets.
These men use it
to great effect,
but as concerns
the alchemy of it,
they're no better-informed
than we are.
We're making the
powder as we speak.
[HARUAKIRA]
Huh?
[KID]
Hm?
[chuckling]
[HARUAKIRA] As I thought.
You're a man of bold ideas.
Drifters have brought new
weapons into this realm before.
But with your daring,
you could alter the very
course of this world's history.
Guess primer's
all we're lackin'.
'N what's that?
See, when you hit the
tail-end of a bullet,
the primer's what
sparks the powder.
It appears this substance is a
chemical mixture distinct
from the powder it lights.
We've been researching it,
but to no avail.
C'mon, Abe no Seimei!
Get it done!
I know you're good for it!
[HARUAKIRA] If this were
a question of magic,
I could be of use.
I believe a chemist is
better suited for this task.
Oh dear, have you
caught a cold?
My poor, sniffly contessa!
[BOTH] Is there no justice
in this terrible world?
[ELF GUARD A]
Bring it to a halt!
[ELF GUARD B]
Stop, damn you!
Who are you with?
[gasps] My greetings.
Any chance the Drifters
are here with you?
[ELF GUARD C gasps]
[SEMU]
I'm with the Octobrists.
[MARK] Yeah, the guys
with the Bland Master!
[MASHA]
I think it's Grand.
[SEMU] Is anyone
here called, "Boob Dream"?
Huh?
Do you mean...?
[HARUAKIRA] You say you're
making black powder.
Is that true?
[NOBUNAGA]
Yes. Now we wait on sulfur.
I asked your busty
subordinate about it.
[SEMU]
Grand Master, sir!
[HARUAKIRA]
Semu! Why are you--?
I brought the sulfur,
as requested.
Olmine contacted headquarters
and requisitioned all we had.
It smells of old eggs.
What purpose could it serve?
[MARK]
Ew, farts!
[MASHA]
So much farts!
[NOBUNAGA chuckles]
Three cheers for
that top-heavy girl.
She did exactly as I bade.
Remind me to honk her
chest as a thank you.
Now we have everything.
The Dwarves will be next!
[HARUAKIRA]
For all of his usefulness,
Nobunaga may be a threat.
I may need to put
him under watch,
lest he turn our
world atop its head.
That which makes
Drifters extraordinary
also makes it hard to
bend them to one's will.
The Ends act in sync.
All serving their master's
quest to destroy this world.
Our heroes are
truly a wildcard!
The man who created
the Orte Empire;
he was probably one of them.
The founding of the nation
was likely a noble act,
undertaken to help
the downtrodden.
He took a people whose
spirit had been crushed
and gave them pride.
But it emboldened them to
pursue decades of conquest.
For better or worse,
they're unpredictable.
I wonder if that's the reason
you've brought them here,
Murasaki.
[NOBUNAGA] Oh-ho!
Breathe in that fragrance!
[HARUAKIRA] So, Nobunaga.
What's next in your master plan?
Free the Elves from their
bondage, make black powder,
it doesn't end there.
I'm sure you have
something in mind, sir.
[NOBUNAGA]
Simple. We free the Dwarves.
[gasps]
Our forces will drift
from place to place, see.
Liberating the demi-humans
and then forming alliances.
We'll cut the Orte
off at the knees.
We'll gather manpower
and mass-produce guns
with which to arm them
and wipe their empire
off the face of the map!
We'll unite the tribes,
but let each people rule itself.
We'll keep the armies
on a leash, of course.
And appoint Toyohisa to lead,
like a shogun above his daimyo.
If our luck holds out,
we'll use the precepts of
bushido to establish order.
This is our path to victory.
It's the only way
we'll have enough
military might at our disposal.
There's no other way
to beat the Ends.
We must have a standing army,
made of those we've freed
from their shackles!
[HARUAKIRA]
If the army's too strong,
then freedom will suffer for it!
Self-government will fail!
There's a danger in
what you propose!
Do not discount it!
It'll be a damn sight better
than what they have right now.
[NOBUNAGA speaking Orte]
You wait and see, Abe no Seimei.
[HARUAKIRA] He's learned the
Elven tongue in so short a time?
Who is this man?
[NOBUNAGA] Not to brag, but I'm
a person of singular ambition.
In the end, this world will
thank me for taking charge!
All of the demi-humans will
have a place at the table!
Thriving business
and fair taxes.
Living in comfort.
Well-trained army.
Our nation will be a utopia!
You have my guarantee.
Why? Why do you want Toyohisa
to serve as the overlord?
What do you gain by
not doing it yourself?
[NOBUNAGA]
Frankly,
I'm not cut from the right sort
of cloth to lead a nation.
[NOBUNAGA] I thought by
assuming the worst of men,
I could see into their motives.
However, the hearts of men
don't seem to be
such a tidy affair.
That's why I was overthrown.
Fifty years of life and what
do I have to show for it all?
In the land of our birth,
when Honno-ji temple
was set to the torch
and I had to stare
betrayal in the face,
the person I first suspected...
...was my own son.
But Nobutada died in battle,
thinking he followed me
to the grave. I'm a fool.
Unfit for the mantle
of supreme leader.
On the other hand,
Toyohisa doesn't give a damn
about what he gains or loses!
He acts with brutal purity!
That said, he'll benefit from
wise council. Like mine.
[TOYOHISA]
Which is it?
The ravages of time?
Or an act?
We must defend Carthage!
If we are not vigilant,
it will fall to the enemy!
Ah, my young brother Magon!
Round up the elephants!
I wish to cross the Alps on them
and blacken the eye of Rome!
[TOYOHISA] Whoever you're
yelling about isn't here.
My name is Shimazu Toyohisa.
[HANNIBAL] Huh?
My wife's brother, Hasdrubal?
How could you abandon
your duties, man?
Carthago Nova needs you!
[HANNIBAL growls]
[yells]
[gasps]
Did you really think I would let
Carthage fall without
putting up a fight?
I will repel you so long as
I have the breath to do it.
I'd not forget a face
like yours, Marcus.
Or Valerius. Suddenly I'm not
so sure which one you are.
Well, seems it's not an act.
But there is still
a spark to you.
I wonder what must you've been
like in your prime, graybeard.
I imagine you were the
bane of all you fought.
W-What's going on over here?
Are you all right?
We're fine!
[OLMINU gasps]
Watch over this
tricky old man.
There's something about his eyes
that reminds me of my uncle.
[gasps]
I aim to free the Dwarves next!
[ELVES gasp]
Did he say Dwarves?
Dirty bastards!
You've gotta be kidding!
I'm not risking my life
for one of them!
That's right!
We're under no obligation to go
to them in their time of aid!
[ELVES chattering]
[SHARA]
Toyohisa, a word, if I may?
Elves and Dwarves
hate each other.
Since time immemorial,
there has been bad blood
between our peoples.
We've never been able to
find a common ground.
When the Orte invaded our lands,
the Dwarves didn't lift a
finger to try and help us.
How can you ask us to take
up arms in their name?
I'm not askin'
for a damn thing.
Come with me or don't,
I go either way!
Not so fast!
Hold on, Toyohisa!
Turn around. I'm not kidding.
I've got plans in motion!
You're risking everything!
Agh! That idiot!
Why does he do whatever
the hell he wants to?!
Why don't you
listen to your elders?!
This one, at least! Agh!
[FIZONA ELF A]
What now, Shara?
Do you think he
can do it himself?
[SHARA]
Hm... Maybe.
But we're not about
to let that happen.
He saved our village
from massacre.
When the Orte first attacked,
if the Elves or Dwarves had
reached out to the other one,
we could've joined forces
and repelled the invasion.
If we'd worked together,
perhaps we'd have
been free all this time.
Tonight we can
make the choice
our elders should've
made 40 years ago.
You're going, then?
You fly to your
target like an arrow.
But what sends you
from the bowstring?
Do you want to change the world,
like the wily Nobunaga?
[TOYOHISA]
Their heads.
Huh?
I'm from Satsuma,
so taking a foe's head
is worth risking my life.
Care to join the fun?
[gasps]
Ha! This Japanese fella's
right entertainin'!
It's tempting,
but we need to hurry
back to headquarters.
The search for Scipio
continues apace,
and we need to keep
an eye on the movement
of Drifters and Ends alike.
You have your work
and I have mine.
Would you take
Olmine with you?
I believe she's
proven her worth.
[NOBUNAGA]
Wait, wait, wait! Come on!
Wait up, Toyohisa!
Hello, beautiful!
Is my dinner ready yet?
You already ate and I'm
still not a girl, sir!
I didn't ask for this!
How stupid are you?!
They come because they want to,
or they don't come at all.
It's pointless if I force them.
[HARUAKIRA gasps]
We're gathering men to help!
Let the villages know!
[chuckles] The lad's smarter
than I give him credit for!
Boob Dream, make sure
that we're ready to embark.
[BUTCH]
Hey, One-Eyed Jack!
[NOBUNAGA]
Hm?
[BUTCH] Hell, I seen ya
lookin' at it. Call it a gift.
We're gon' leave the
Gatling gun behind,
on account of no ammo.
Even it turns out you're
able to make more
bullets like you
been talkin' 'bout,
maybe you could
return the kindness,
no pressure either way, mind.
All right, you rascal samurai.
Good huntin' to ya.
[chuckles] Look at them.
Warriors down to a man!
[MALE VOICE chants]