[MILLS] Okay, so the
night-soil from the villages
goes to the castle.
Unless they can bring it
straight to us and we store it.
But... then where are the
horses and wheat supposed to go?
[groans] I'm glad they spared
my life and all, but still!
[ELVEN BOY A]
Virgin Man!
I've been looking
all over for you!
For the love of all that's holy,
stop calling me that!
A frilly carriage
is on its way.
Frilly? Like how?
[MILLS] That's the banner
of Count Saint-Germain.
[grunts]
A powerful Orte aristocrat!
[gasps] All you Elf boys,
run for cover! Do it!
Ladies, you're fine.
[ELVEN BOY A]
Why do we have to hide?
[FEMALE ELF GUARD A]
Halt, you!
[SAINT GERMI]
Hm?
[MALE ELF GUARD A]
Stay back!
[FEMALE ELF GUARD A]
Wh-What do you want with us?
[SAINT GERMI]
I could die of boredom here.
I'm already fading away.
[ALLISTER] Not much of a feast
for the senses, now is it?
I thought the abode
of the Elves
would be a far
more magical milieu!
Sunlight streaming down
through a canopy of
branches overhead,
and then we see them!
Naked Elven boys frolicking
with no sense of shame!
[BOTH]
Oh the thought of it!
Do stop.
[MILLS]
Count Saint-Germain!
What could bring a
person of your eminence
to a place like this one?
You! Drab little man.
Are you a Drifter?
No, I'm very much not.
I am Mills, former auditor to
Orte's Elven colonies, milord.
Now I work for my
captors under duress.
[SAINT GERMI] Hmm. A virgin,
from the looks of it.
I'm here for the Drifters,
you milksop.
You would do well
to produce them.
I'm not a man you deny.
You heard the contessa,
Drifters, tout-de-suite!
[ALLISTER] There is a marked
lack of Elf boys prancing about!
Remedy this at once,
or taste of my wrath!
Well, the Drifters
aren't here right now.
[ALL]
Huh?
[SAINT GERMI] What do you mean
they aren't here right now?!
Where else could they be?!
Answer me, virgin,
or I'll devour you whole!
I'm sorry, but they're away!
They went off to
free the Dwarves
and they took the
Elven men along
and they hope to have the
Dwarves construct firearms
for them and I really
wish you'd stop gnawing
on my head, milord!
[SAINT GERMI gasps]
Did you just say they're
going to have the Dwarves
build them guns?!
Well, what about...
What about the black powder?!
They already have black powder.
They're making a ton
of it all the time.
[SAINT GERMI] That's it, Orte.
You had a damn good run.
Who on earth are these
other-worldly opportunists?
The mustachioed demi-god
was trouble enough,
but this, it sets
my head a-spin.
You dolt, Murasaki,
what the hell have you done?!
This whole thing's a disaster!
Dear, contesa, let me set
you mind at ease!
Murasaki? Who's that?
It's none of you concern.
Don't pry, underlings. Hm.
I'll grace you with
my August presence
until they make thier return.
And will betide you if you don't
give me the royal treatment,
virgin.
[growls]
[BRONZE DRAGON]
Behold, the Black King
and his motley court.
The doom of all mankind;
Or so your boasting
would have one believe.
You broke the will of the
lesser lights of our tribe,
reducing proud dragons
to beasts of burden.
Your hubris shall
be your undoing.
[BLACK KING] I am king
and shepherd alike.
If you mean to join my flock,
O serpent, you must submit.
Quiet, fool!
For only a fool would
dare to belittle me thus!
I am the Bronze Dragon!
[BLACK KING] The first shall
be last and the last, first.
You brandish your title,
but alas, it moves me not.
One starving Goblin
child is of like worth.
Turn and face me,
you cocksure lunatic!
I'll tear you to a pulp,
as befits your rags!
[BLACK KING chuckles]
[BRONZE DRAGON]
What is this?
[BRONZE DRAGON yells]
[BLACK KING] Do you join
our brotherhood this night,
or die a prince of your kind?
I would have
your answer, serpent.
Life or death. Your choice.
[BRONZE DRAGON]
I submit to you!
Just stop! Make it stop!
[BRONZE DRAGON yells]
[BRONZE DRAGON]
Your patchwork confederacy,
I will join it.
[BLACK KING] It is a
pearl of great worth.
An object of fear no longer.
Your flesh has betrayed you.
And hence you are welcome,
fellow outcast.
The sight of it
stills the heart.
It must be something if it moves
you to speak up, Hijikata.
Our lord can orchestrate the
replication of life itself.
The power to heal is but one
movement in that symphony.
What is cancer,
but living tissue given
over to ruinous zeal?
[GOBLINS speaking Orte]
[BLACK KING] Please, brothers,
kneel not at my approach.
Merely grant me space to
set my talents to use.
[RASPUTIN] Anything organic
falls under his dominion.
He can copy it, ad infinitum.
To those who struggle
against the Black King.
To gaze at such a figure
across the field of battle,
it must turn their blood to
ice to know what he can do.
Instant healing to his
injured soldiers, however dire.
Even those with one
foot in the grave
make a quick return
to the front line.
Firewood and foodstuffs
multiply at his merest touch.
It's that largesse that
puzzles me the most.
Why does he have his
creatures till the earth?
To what end, when he could
feed them all forever?
[BLACK KING] Simple. God may
reign for time eternal,
but I claim no such tenure.
Greetings, milord.
[BLACK KING]
Your work, Rasputin.
How fares it?
[exhales] This field is
still a passion of mine.
It's a little threadbare
as religions go,
but that could be a virtue.
given our simple audience.
For our symbol,
I chose the eye.
Fire-worship serves as
the cauldron in which
I mixed a syncretic
stew of Vedic,
Egyptian, and Celtic myths.
On the language front.
We're giving them a
simplified written alphabet.
But I expect integration of
this to take quite some time.
[BLACK KING] And how will
you foster a sense of unity?
My people have
precious little in common.
Goblins and Kobolds today,
but in the time to come,
many will join us.
We need to be a haven for all.
They will speak as one.
They will work towards
their mutual betterment.
And when they worship, their
acts of devotion will all align.
Thus will those
branded monsters,
forge a new civilization, and
cast humanity into the dust.
[gasps]
Where am I?
[ANASTASIA]
Awake, at long last.
What happened?
He beat you.
The dragon cavalry
brought you here.
[JOAN OF ARC grunts]
What of Gilles?!
[ANASTASIA] They killed him.
He's nothing but salt now.
[JOAN OF ARC gasps, grunts]
What will you do?
They will burn!
All of them!
Nyet, Joan.
You underestimated them.
And it nearly cost your life.
[JOAN OF ARC grunts]
This time I'll kill them!
I'll blacken their bones!
Blood for blood!
This is my right!
[ANASTASIA]
Silence.
[ANASTASIA] You will be patient.
And when the time is right,
I will help you to slake
your thirst for their blood.
[JOAN OF ARC grunts]
Drifter Bastard.
When I find you,
you will burn.
What a sight it will make!
Your face melting away
from your very skull!
[RASPUTIN]
How did it go, Princess?
She is awake at last.
Miraculous for one whose
skull took such a blow.
The Black Lord himself
tended to her wound.
I'm just surprised she didn't
succumb to her injuries
while en route.
[RASPUTIN] The Drifter leader,
that samurai Toyohisa.
I am surprised he would spare
a foe simply for being a woman.
Maybe he went easy on her.
Who can say?
He fought with her, but he
refused to finish her off.
Instead he brained her
and left her in a well,
still quite alive.
These are the acts
of a contradictory man.
Thus behaves their
warrior caste.
They elude all understanding.
Eight hundred years
of their feudal system
and still they just
murder each other
for the same
tiny specks of earth
amid the waters of the Pacific.
Yet their descendants defeated
our Russia in battle!
His treatment of Joan has
struck a nerve with you.
Hasn't it, Princess?
You forget yourself, monk.
[RASPUTIN]
A thousand pardons.
[BRONZE DRAGON]
Mercy!
Stop this! I beg of you!
This is torment!
Black King! Mercy!
End this butchery!
I'm sorry! I submit!
[BLACK KING] The scales fall
from your eyes too late, dragon.
[KOBOLD A grunts]
[BLACK KING]
Silence, my child.
Well? Which are you?
A Drifter, or an End?
[EASY] That self-righteous
Murasaki acts so important,
when really he's just a
dead-weight desk-jockey!
No way am I gonna
lose to that jackass!
[DWARVES chatter]
[sighs]
What the hell is a "muckit"?
They go well with grog?
Toss one on my plate!
[NOBUNAGA]
Musket, damn it! It's a weapon!
Hell. All you
moochers do is eat!
[DWARF CHIEF] We'll give
'em hell, weakened as we are!
Tall one, bring us
more booze and meat!
Yeah, I think your people
have had quite enough.
Whadja say? We were
at death's door!
[OLMINU] There should be
enough food in this storehouse
to keep us all
victualed for weeks.
You've gotta be kidding me.
I'm sorry, Olmine, but they're
clamoring for more!
Hot soup! For a hund--!
If they want to keep eating,
maybe they should
cook for themselves!
They're getting more muscular
with every bowl they empty out.
[DWARF A grunts]
You know; it is
impolite to stare.
[ELVES]
Uh-huh.
What are you smiling about?
You almost look nostalgic.
[SHARA]
Hm?
They've finally
made their return.
The Dwarves from our
bedtime stories are back.
What are you doing, man?
How can you stomach a soup
full of beef and horse meat?!
I don't give a damn.
We'd eat meat in Satsuma.
Get hungry enough,
and we'd even cook a dog.
You fill a puppy's belly with
rice and let it cook awhi--
Enough! I don't want to hear it!
[gasps]
Hey! I got somethin'
to get off my chest.
There's this guy I know
named Yoshitsune,
an' he's kind of a rat-bastard.
Are you listenin'?
S'hard to tell with you.
You're sorta hard to ignore.
[YOICHI]
Here's what I don't get.
Outta nowhere,
Yoshitsune tells me to shoot
a fan on one'a
the enemy boats!
Who the hell even asks
for a thing like that?
I mean, I did it, but it
coulda gone either way.
I don't need that
kinda pressure.
Whatever's in that cup,
you should probably
stop drinking it.
Speakin' of booze,
I can put it away, too!
Shut up!
[ALL shouting]
[NOBUNAGA]
Dear faithful of the Oda clan,
this is your departed Daimyo.
I hope this missive find
you well. In retrospect,
I realize how unfailingly
loyal you all were to me.
All except you, Mistuhide.
I'm going to kill you
the first chance I get!
[exhales] Let's have a look
at that "musket," yeah?
[NOBUNAGA]
Just treat it with care.
We ain't gonna break it!
[DWARF B]
An iron tube of some kind.
Mounted onto the wood.
They hot-rolled the iron,
like as not.
[DWARF C] Trigger mechanism's
the same as what ya see
on a crossbow.
That part's simple enough.
[DWARF D] Seems the
spring causes this iron bit
to drop down onto the metal pan.
To what end, I wonder?
And how does the
tube come into play?
[DWARF E] The wood's just wood,
from the sight of it.
[chuckles]
So, what's this posh
walking stick good for?
Uh... killing.
And it does its job well.
Gunpowder ignites at the
one end of the cylinder,
firing a lead bullet
into your foe.
Weaponry! Of course.
Wicked little contraption.
Killing your foe from
afar can be right useful.
But why bother setting tiny
explosions to get it done?
Arrows and crossbows
kill 'em just as dead.
I don't see the need
for this frippery.
I'm a bit confused on that
point myself, Lord Nobunaga.
Bows are silent, and fall well
within our means to make,
so why this passion
for the musket?
Well... uh...
The noise and smoke
both play a role.
How do I put it?
[TOYOHISA] A musket's battle-cry
can freeze your blood.
You compound the terror
with every bullet fired.
And it's an easy
weapon to pick up.
Arm peasants at dawn,
and they can kill trained
soldiers by nightfall.
[NOBUNAGA] Yes, as I thought,
the lad's no fool.
But fighting is all he knows.
Their range and stopping power
are impressive, sure.
But muskets are a boon
for more than those alone.
They make killing so easy.
The merest twitch of a finger.
In a land with muskets,
anyone can take
to the battlefield.
A nation at the ready,
all citizens primed for combat.
That part I'd be wise
to keep to myself.
[hammers clanging]
[BOTH gasp]
Masters of
their trade, they are.
[gasps]
What's that?
I've been eyeing
this iron cylinder.
From the muckit
or what-have-ya.
The blacksmiths of your
country are no joke,
anyone can see that.
But, there's no
bestin' a Dwarf.
Here. Give it a look.
Wha-- You mean to tell
me you've made one?
I showed it to
you yesterday!
[DWARF CHIEF]
Schematic would've been
a different kettle of fish, but
you brought us the real thing.
Easy to figure it out
when you're holdin' onto it.
Give it a try. Should work
as well as that original.
[NOBUNAGA]
If all the forges in this place
were brought up
to full efficiency,
how many of these
could we make?
This town kept more'n half of
their soldiers clad and armed,
and that with us starving.
Giving the task our best effort,
that'll be a better
situation for all involved.
Let's see, then...
Can't forget there will be
a bit of a learning curve.
Little trickier then
a halberd or sword.
Seven or eight's feasible.
Maybe ten, once we've really
hit our stride with 'em.
That's the best you can do?
Not even a dozen muskets?
What do you want, man?
Ten muckits a day is plenty!
No need to dress us down!
[NOBUNAGA]
A day?!
I take it all back.
The Dwarves are brilliant!
We can all see that villainous
face you're makin'!
He gets like that
every now and then.
I wouldn't let it worry you any.
[NOBUNAGA]
Tell me, where is Toyohisa?
Stuffing his face again?
[YOICHI]
I'm not sure what he's up to.
Oh. The hot-headed one
gathered up our young men.
Said he wanted to work the
food off. Practice a little.
How on earth he was able
to guess which of you
Dwarves are young,
I'll never understand.
You all look old to me.
Is that a curse?
Go to hell!
We're no strangers to war!
Every blow is lethal
when a Dwarf fights!
We put all of our passion into
one swing of the battleaxe!
That strike was the Jigen-style.
Didn't think I'd see it here.
Uh, Jigen? Never heard of it.
A type of swordplay.
It was popular among the
young men in my province.
I didn't have time to pursue it.
I was busy enough trying to
master the Taisha style.
[DWARF F] However wide the gulf
is between my world and yours,
in battle, we are one.
Though in looks they may differ,
every land has its warriors.
[ALLISTER]
Beautifully said.
[DWARF F]
What the devil?
[DWARF G] Hold on!
Are they women? I can't tell!
[ALLISTER] Forging an alliance
not only with the Elves,
but with these
swarthy fellows, too?
You cut right to the chase,
you saucy Drifters!
[SAINT GERMI] In my wildest
flights of fancy...
[ALL]
Hm?
...I never expected
you to copy a musket.
How it sets my heart aflutter!
The hell are you?
Who is this jester?
[SAINT GERMI]
Goodness! How rustic.
W-We have a
big problem, everyone!
Saint-Germain's
wagon is outside.
[panting] That flouncing
friend of the Empire!
Mouthy little girl!
Hey, Boob-Dream.
What's wrong with this man?
Is he an actor? I know the type.
This is Count Saint-Germain!
A full third of the Orte Empire
sits beneath his thumb!
What are you doing here?
I traveled all the way to
the deserted castle
for a rendezvous, but you left
me writhing in anticipation
with naught but
a virgin for a host.
Have you any idea what
torture is was for a person
of my pedigree
and refinement
cooling my heels
amid the hoy beloy.
You're lucky that I came at all.
[OLMINU] Tell us the truth!
Are you a Drifter, too?
Or do you side with the Ends?
Oh, stop!
I'm not some peasant
you can just accuse.
I'm a Drifter, not that I
expect you to believe it.
Have you ever seen an
End of this caliber?
[gasps]
[SAINT GERMI chuckles]
Your mind's as empty
as your shirt is full,
top-heavy cow.
But why did you help
found Orte, then?
How could a Drifter do that?
Bite your tongue, you!
Do you really think the
Ends have the wherewithal
to create a nation
on par with this one?
Adolph Hitler was a Drifter,
and I defy you to show
me a finer specimen!
The government he
created here as Father
was the model of efficiency.
It was ruthless
and lean and pure,
like nothing you've ever seen!
He bent the chaos into order
through sheer force of will.
The people took pride
in their country,
buoyed by this
new sense of self.
And I took my 30% finder's fee.
We did incredible work,
ol' Dolphy and I.
We made a kingdom that's
been at perpetual war
for 50 years and
ever the victor!
Your eyes...
They remind me of
a man I once knew.
He was sly and when
he took his own life,
he filled a flawless
teapot full of gunpowder
and blew it to hell,
just to spite me.
He was a lunatic, too.
[SAINT GERMI laughs]
Oh, how terrible! You lump me
in with Matsunaga Hisahide?
Cut me to the quick!
[NOBUNAGA]
He already knows about us?
If so, we must be vigilant.
So. What brought you out here,
Count Saint-Germain?
[SAINT GERMI]
I came to judge whether
you're worth my switching
partners mid-dance again.
You are the Drifter leader,
Shimazu Toyohisa, are you not?
That I am!
And much like the fire-witch,
I can't tell your gender.
Who are you, stranger?
Are you a man of Orte?
A man of Orte?
If you want to know,
allow me to give you...
...a closer look!
[ALLISTER]
He saw it coming!
[TOYOHISA] Quick with a blade,
but no heart behind it.
Why're you here?
It's a pity, sir.
Thirty years on, you would be
slaying me with but a glance!
Youth does nothing for me.
Apologies if I split
you stem to stern.
You'd be safe if you
were a grizzled old wolf
in the full bloom
of your maturity,
but sadly you are not!
[gasps]
[HANNIBAL grunts]
[ALLISTER gasps]
Hey there, greybeard!
Allister! Speak to me!
I am undone, Fulame!
You've killed him with
your come-hither stare!
What does that mean, even?
[FULAME] Luckily, you and the
geezer leave my loins cold!
I'm immune to your man-magic!
[FULAME grunts]
For Allister!
Nothing can stop me
but a ponytailed boy
with hair over one eye,
and what are the odds of
anyone matching all that?
Toyohisa. A word, if I may?
[shouts]
[SAINT GERMI] By now, my valets
are testing your leader.
Pray that he passes muster,
lest they leave him a corpse.
Though, I'll have
my answer either way.
[FULAME groans]
Contessa!
Help us, Your Loveliness!
[ALLISTER grunts]
That's enough outta you two!
Toyohisa, how'd it go?
The training? Fine. I mean,
except for these fops.
And again I don't know if
I'm allowed to take a head.
Who's this one?
[SAINT GERMI]
I am a turncoat.
Why should I believe it?
[SAINT GERMI] It's true.
I come bearing gifts.
The Empire on a silver platter.
I suppose you could call
it a dowry of sorts.
Dowry?
Silver platter?
Hear me out, gentle folk.
A nation is much like
a tree being cut down.
If it's carelessly felled,
what remains is useless.
If other countries
should smell the blood,
they'll set at Orte
like it's a suckling pig.
They'll carve up the
kingdom and trundle home,
leaving a carcass in their wake.
All right, so what
do you have in mind?
Why throw in with us?
We need to topple
Orte with a single blow,
while it still
projects the illusion
of strength and unassailability
to its neighbors.
Interested?
[MALE VOICE chants]