[HARUAKIRA] I trust you've
made progress, Kafet. Report.
[KAFET]
Affirmative, Grand Master.
I brought the two of them here,
as you bade me.
The Drifters are both men.
Quite advanced in
years to look at them.
And both at each
other's throats.
What could I have done
to merit the hell of being
marooned with this
thieving Roman?
[SCIPIO grunts]
I didn'ta steal your tactics!
I built upon your rude maneuver,
thus refining it into
something new entirely!
You're a thief!
You never would
have thought of that
two-front attack formation
you used at Zama,
if I hadn't crushed you with
it at Cannae, you dog!
History will remember
me as a tactical genius!
To the victor goes the spoils!
Oh, really? I don't
seem to recall you
crossing the Alps
on an elephant!
That damnable gimmick is
all you ever go on about!
[BOTH grunting]
[HANNIBAL] If I had an
elephant right now,
I'd show you a gimmick!
[SCIPIO]
When I get back,
I'll salt your
precious Carthage!
[HANNIBAL]
When I get back,
I'll sack Rome and
piss in the Tiber!
[KAFET] What would you have
me do next, Grand Master?
[HARUAKIRA]
Stop them.
Yes, sir. As you wish.
[HARUAKIRA]
These Drifters are as powerful
as they are enigmatic.
We don't know what
they aim to do.
We must learn of
their intentions.
Fail at this task,
and the world we know
will be annihilated.
[SHARA speaking Orte]
[speaking Orte]
[NOBUNAGA, TOYOHISA snoring]
So, you noticed, too?
[TOYOHISA]
I smell it,
but I can't make it out.
There's carnage
in the air tonight.
[grunts]
Something's burning. I'd wager
it's the nearby village.
Bandits must have
set fire to the place.
The Elves are under attack.
That's what you're smelling.
[TOYOHISA]
What are "Elves"?
They're an odd little folk
who live beyond the
edge of the forest.
As it turns out,
it was two of them who dragged
you here as you were dying.
[NOBUNAGA]
Hey!
Dammit, Toyohisa!
What are you doing?
I don't know what this
place is, or how I got here!
Maybe this is a fever-dream,
or maybe I'm a corpse!
But, alive or dead,
Shimazu Toyohisa can fight!
And he's off,
running into trouble.
Never mind the fact you just
stitched him back together.
He's got the temperament
of a musket ball.
[YOICHI chuckles]
[chuckles]
[OLMINU] Does this
mean they're mobilizing?
[NOBUNAGA]
Onward!
Look at them go!
What do they mean to do?
[gasps]
[TOYOHISA] Good of you
to join us, Nobunaga!
Should we slow down?
I thought the Demon
King of the Sixth
Heaven would be
lighter on his feet!
Bastard! We'll see how fast you
run when you're pushing fifty!
And how old are you,
Lord Toyohisa?
Thirty, you?
[chuckles]
What're you laughin' about?
I'm still in the
bloom of youth, imp!
The histories left out the part
where Yoichi was a huge dick!
[gasps]
[BOTH panting]
[speaking Orte]
[whimpers]
[BOTH panting]
[gasps]
[ORTE SOLDIERS gasp]
[TOYOHISA]
So, yeah. I'm feeling better.
[yelling, grunting]
I'm gonna cut your
head clean off!
[speaking Orte]
Your words don't make any sense.
I have no idea what the hell
you're trying to say to me.
Tell me again in my language!
[grunting]
[TOYOHISA] Addressing me in a
foreign tongue is an insult!
A mortal one!
[grunts]
[screams]
[TOYOHISA growls]
[BOTH whimper]
Heh! Yeah, you two
are odd little folk.
[whimpering continues]
[TOYOHISA] If you hadn't
dragged me to my countrymen,
I'd be dead.
Saving your lives was
the least I could do!
[MASHA gasps]
Well, you seem to have
adopted a softer tone.
[TOYOHISA]
Huh?
You just killed
that soldier
for the sin of not
speaking like us.
Quite hypocritical,
don't you think?
[TOYOHISA growls]
Repeat the following!
"Help me, Toyohisa!
You're my only hope!"
[MASHA, MARK]
Huh?
Say the damn words!
"Help me, Toyohisa!"
[BOTH] "Help me, Toyohisa!"
There, ya see?
That wasn't so hard, was it?
Please do not poke fun
at him like that again.
And the worst part is,
you can tell he's so
damn proud of himself.
[NOBUNAGA] Barring heads,
they're all well-equipped.
No raggedy band of
half-armored raiders, this.
Actual soldiers.
The lord's forces, perhaps?
[NOBUNAGA]
Amateurs.
It's like they're asking me
to seize their domain.
[NOBUNAGA]
I've made my decision, you two.
It's time for us to
take the village.
[HARUAKIRA] Hold on.
Did he say "take"?
[OLMINU]
Yes.
[HARUAKIRA]
He could have said
"retake," or "reclaim,"
or "take back," but no...
It's a part of their nature,
down to the bones.
Their fatal flaw, and their
greatest strength.
Rather, It is the only
strength they possess.
No matter his place in history,
man has one animus that
guides him. One urge, above all.
He desires conquest,
for good or ill.
[ARAM speaking Orte]
[ELFS grunting]
[speaking Orte]
[gasps]
[groans]
[speaking Orte]
[screams]
[growls]
[speaking Orte]
[SHARA grunts]
[ORTE SOLDIER F speaking Orte]
[ARAM speaking Orte]
[speaking Orte]
Why did you burn their wheat?
[NOBUNAGA] Simple. A man can
endure the loss of dignity,
so long as his hunger's met.
And on the other hand,
hunger is nothing to a
man who has dignity.
When you take away both,
when they're scared and
have nothing to lose,
that's when people rise up.
Those rabble-rousing monks
used this trick against
me back in the day.
It's a good way
to steal a country
out from under someone.
[chuckles]
Aren't you a frightening one?
Oh, but those bastards
got what they deserved.
Burned every last
one at Nagashima.
[NOBUNAGA laughs]
[speaking Orte]
[ARAM gasps]
[TOYOHISA]
One!
[ARAM speaking ORTE]
[ALL gasp]
[TOYOHISA grunts]
[TOYOHISA]
Two!
[ORTE SOLDIERS grunt]
[TOYOHISA]
Three!
[ORTE SOLDIERS gasp]
[speaking ORTE]
[grunting]
[TOYOHISA]
Four!
[ALL gasp]
You there, in the cape.
You've a good head
on your shoulders.
A commander's head.
How 'bout... you leave it
here for my collection?
[speaking Orte]
[MASHA speaking Orte]
[gasps]
[BOTH speaking Orte]
[speaking Orte]
[MARK speaking Orte]
[TOYOHISA grunts]
[ELF FATHER sobs]
[growls]
How dare you?
How dare you slaughter
the unarmed?
[chuckles]
[TOYOHISA] I don't
want your head anymore.
I wanna send your soul to hell!
[speaking Orte]
[TOYOHISA grunts]
[gasps]
[BOTH grunting]
Down... you... go!
[grunting]
Too easy! Waste of my time!
[whimpers]
[speaking Orte]
[grunts]
[ARAM whimpers]
[ARAM grunts, shouts]
[ALL gasping]
[ARAM gurgles]
[NOBUNAGA] The boy
knows how to fight.
Using his scabbard in lieu
of a sword? Such brutality!
[gasps]
What a sight!
Glad he's on our side.
Have you finished your task?
Indeed. His minions fled in
the dark, but I found them.
Toyohisa may scare his foe,
but your foe never
sees you coming.
[NOBUNAGA]
All right, then.
How's this puppet
show gonna end?
[ARAM continues grunting]
--[TOYOHISA grunts]
--[neck crackles]
[speaking Orte]
[ELVES gasp]
[sobs]
[TOYOHISA exhales]
[ELVES gasping]
[gasps]
[TOYOHISA]
Take it.
[ELF FATHER gasps]
[TOYOHISA]
End his life.
[whimpers]
He has to die! By your hand!
Pick up that sword and sheathe
it in that villain's heart!
I don't know a
thing about you,
whether you were a
good father or bad!
All I know is your son
lies dead at your feet!
You couldn't save his life,
but you can avenge it!
[ELVES gasp]
[NOBUNAGA] His words
remain a riddle to them,
but when it comes to his intent,
no way can they plead ignorance.
[chuckles]
Quite a man, that one.
[ELF FATHER whimpers]
[ARAM groans]
[speaking Orte]
[ARAM yells]
[ELF FATHER sobs]
For your son.
Good work.
'Sup!
Where the hell were
you durin' all that?
I still got thread
holdin' me together!
We were busy, doin' stuff.
Busy! What he said!
Bet you're beat!
Please, make yourself comfy
on this nearby wooden crate!
Take a load off,
Toyohisa, my man.
You've earned it,
with your heroics tonight.
[TOYOHISA grunts]
[OLMINU]
I can't believe it!
I'm seeing it,
but how's it possible?
The three Drifters took on a
knight and his foot soldiers...
...and killed the bunch!
[TOYOHISA]
Hmph.
[MURASAKI]
Hm.
[MALE VOICE chants]
[EASY] Look at you
with your little desk.
Quite the heroic figure
you're cutting there.
Push that boulder for as
long as you like, Murasaki.
You can throw the best possible
examples of humanity into play.
When all's said and done,
I'll be the winner.
Pardon my French,
but you're pissing in the wind.
Deep down, I think you
know that I'm right.
[MURASAKI]
Get out of here, EASY.
Their are wrongs
that must be righted
[EASY grunts]
Go ahead, scowl at me. But I am
not letting you have your way.
[gasps]
[MURASAKI]
Leave this place, wretch.
[growls]
You're quick with the
big talk, Murasaki.
If you think you can
outmaneuver me,
go ahead and try!
[MURASAKI gasps]
My Ends are gonna
massacre your Drifters.
I so look forward to showing you
your heroes' heads on pikes!
[OLMINU] This is Olmine!
Repeat, this is Olmine!
Grand Master,
the trio of Drifters
just claimed the
village of Elves!
It's dangerous to
let them run riot!
Give me the order to
bring them in, sir!
Negative, Olmine.
There's no time for that.
Do not bring them here.
Keep your distance.
[OLMINU]
What? You... you mean?
That's right. The die is cast.
The battle is about to begin!
[MALE VOICE chants]