[ORTE SOLDIERS chattering]
It's empty.
There's no one
in here, either.
The Elves are gone!
[ORTE COMMANDER] They're up
to something, but what?
Commander! You should see this!
What is it?
In the well.
[groans] Why does it
smell like shit over here?
The Elves.
They've contaminated their own
water-supply with their filth.
And that's not the
strangest part of it.
[ORTE COMMANDER]
Go on.
[VICE COMMANDER] Well,
they've dug out the contents
of the communal toilet, sir.
It's empty.
Do you mean to tell me
the Elves took their shit
along with them?
What the hell are
they playing at?
Where could they've gone?
None of it makes sense!
[TOYOHISA] After dark,
every soldier's life is forfeit.
All those heads are coming off.
[NOBUNAGA] Twenty swords and
sets of armor from the dead.
A decent haul.
And two horses. Not that
Elves know how to ride.
Thankfully, I've got
a plan for them.
The armor's not much of a boon.
As a group, they're pretty
inept with a sword.
Oddly enough,
they're damn savants when it
comes to fashioning bows.
Yoichi's there to help, but it
comes to them naturally.
They're happy. Like it
scratches some nagging itch.
Honestly, any one of them
could've given my bowmen
a run for their money.
Swords won't win us the day,
but spears we can't do without.
The longer they are,
the braver the Elves will be.
Even a peasant can
dispatch a samurai
if you give 'em the right tool.
[chuckles]
The news wouldn't
have reached you here.
Akechi Mitsuhide was killed
by peasants in Fushimi,
armed as you describe.
Ha! Did they! Hope they
stabbed him right in that
kumquat-lookin' head of his!
To show my thanks,
they can skip payin' tax
for the rest o' forever.
Looks to me like you
enjoy the scheming
more than you enjoy
the fight itself.
Battles are the just
the bloody afterthought
to the moves
you've already made.
Ya hand your foe his
defeat in moments like this,
well before the carnage.
Ah, Hideyoshi,
only you comprehended
that truth of warcraft.
[chuckles]
So that's why we haven't
seen dead soldiers around!
They were all brought here!
Take whatever you like.
And try not to mind the blood.
[ELVES]
Huh?
Once you've scrubbed
away that gore,
they're basically
as good as new.
[SHARA groans]
That one's dripping with it!
[ELF A]
How much armor is that?
[YOICHI] Telling them
the corpses' fate
would only upset them more.
Toyohisa gathered the heads
and buried them with
all due ceremony.
But their bodies
went to Nobunaga.
[NOBUNAGA] Good that you paid
respect to the enemy dead.
They'll get the chance to fight
again, if all goes as planned.
[OLMINU groans]
[TOYOHISA]
I can smell the decay.
You're making saltpeter?
[NOBUNAGA] The butchered
bodies will mix with the grass,
dirt, piss, and shit.
We'll have saltpeter
ready for the taking
about two years out from now.
[OLMINU grunts]
[NOBUNAGA] Stole this trick
from those bastard Ikko monks.
We should keep people out of
this part of the woods, I guess.
No point lettin'
pestilence spread.
[OLMINU gulps]
[TOYOHISA] And what about
the Elvin night soil?
[NOBUNAGA] We have plenty
of charcoal, but no sulfur.
Just leave it be for now.
Throwing 'em in that pit?
You desecrated their corpses!
How do you figure?
Full burial treats
them no better.
Maggots and time claim
their due share.
We're just helping
the process along.
[NOBUNAGA chuckles]
Waste not, want not.
[TOYOHISA] I washed those heads;
set their faces at peace.
I even marked the burial site.
In death, I showed
them great respect.
You think I wrong them
by taking the bodies,
leaving them here
amid this filth.
But this is the filth
hiding within each of us.
In what part of us does
the soul take residence?
The seat of thought?
Or the dung-filled
sack below it?
The latter is too
profane to be true.
[OLMINU] I see.
The biggest chasm between
my people and his is
not one of knowledge,
industry, or culture,
but in how they treat death.
[OLMINU gasps]
Hey! Listen up, Boob Dream.
Why do you delight in the
butchering of my name?
I'm stupid for lettin'
it get to me.
I find myself in need of a
certain mineral that often sits
in the shadow of volcanoes.
It's yellow, and smells
like the breezes
that leap out from
your backside.
They call it sulfur.
You got any?
Uh. I don't know what my
backside has to do with it.
What do you even
want the sulfur for?
Not your problem.
Just bring me a lot of it!
I'm sure your tentacle-chest
compatriots would lend a hand!
Who?!
The Octo-Breasts,
or whoever they are!
Octobrists!
Although, I'm sure
they'd help you
track it down if
the price is right.
Have any gold?
Tell those Octo-Breasts
not to be greedy!
I'll pay 'em with interest once
I've conquered a few realms!
Just bring me the
damn sulfur, woman!
[OLMINU] Night soil,
corpses, now sulfur?
What does he mean
to do with it all?
I haven't the foggiest idea!
Goodness! Look at that!
See that? A bull's-eye,
but for a couple of inches.
[ELF C]
My turn! Give it here!
Who would've thought?
Your people are
learning so quickly.
[SHARA chuckles]
There's a knack for archery
knit up in our very flesh.
For the longest time,
we've been forbidden
to even lay our
hands upon a bow.
As children,
before the war started,
we used to practice
shooting quite a lot.
[YOICHI chuckles]
No one likes a braggart.
[SHARA gasps]
[YOICHI]
Heh.
{ELVES gasp]
[YOICHI]
Huh...
[YOICHI chuckles]
[SHARA]
All right, all right.
I daresay you've
made your point!
I don't know
what we did, but...
...we're sorry for it.
Very sorry!
[SHARA] We get it, Yoichi,
you're a peerless archer.
Please stop rubbing
our noses in it!
[ELF B] Aren't we going
to need those arrows?
[TOYOHISA] After dark,
we ambush the village.
Kill every soldier
you lay eyes on!
But the mission doesn't
end with their destruction.
We march straight to the
lord's castle after that...
...and take his very head.
What? We do?
[TOYOHISA]
These two told me something.
The reason why we've seen
no women among their people.
For Elves, the power to mate
comes but once a twelve-month.
When last it dawned,
the lord took all of our
young women as hostages.
[NOBUNAGA]
Ah. I see. So that's their plan.
Whittle your numbers down to
nothing through slow attrition.
Fight to save your
wives and children!
Have the courage to
look beyond your cages!
Find the men who've
reduced you to livestock
and bleed them
for their villainy!
If right and wrong can be
said to exist, this is right!
If they strike you dead,
you look your
forefathers in the eye...
...and tell 'em
you died fighting!
You died for the honor
of your families!
Redeem your wives and daughters!
Free them from their bondage!
Reclaim your people's home!
Reclaim your soul!
[NOBUNAGA] This man before me
is a warrior down to his bones.
His sword-work is impeccable,
but his greatest
skill resides within.
When he speaks his heart,
men would follow him to hell.
What a fire he kindles.
[scoffs] Where did the
Elves run off to, I wonder?
I dunno.
Word is, we're searching a
nearby village for 'em tomorrow.
If they're hiding 'em, maybe
we can kill those Elves too.
[laughs]
[ORTE SOLDIER E]
Hope so.
My mouth's dry as dust.
No point in complaining.
The wells are fouled.
Damn those Long Ears,
throwing shit into
their own water.
I say we cut open
the lot of 'em,
their manhoods to their chins!
[gasps]
[TOYOHISA grunting]
[ORTE SOLDIER I]
The hell? What's happening?
[ORTE SOLDIERS grunting]
They're attacking!
[VICE COMMANDER]
We've got 'em cornered!
[gasps]
H-He's a Drifter!
[TOYOHISA]
You ready? Come at me!
[gasps]
D-Don't let him get away!
After him!
[ORTE SOLDIERS shouting]
I knew the Elves could never
do this without assistance.
[VICE COMMANDER] No matter
what it takes, cut him down!
[ORTE SOLDIER A]
Get him!
[ORTE SOLDIER B]
Where'd he go?
[NOBUNAGA]
Excellent!
They've taken the bait.
Does everyone know their role?
[horses whine]
[NOBUNAGA] In battle,
speed is the greatest virtue.
Stick to the plan and you'll
come through this just fine.
And even if you
make a hash of it,
all you lose is your life!
Could be worse, right?
[ELVES grunt]
[NOBUNAGA]
Keep running!
Not the 200,000
I used to lead into battle,
but they'll do for now.
[NOBUNAGA laughs]
For all of its flaws, and life
has many, it's never dull.
[gasps]
[ORTE SOLDIER C]
There he is!
[ORTE COMMANDER]
What are you doing?
It's one of him
against all of you!
Catch him and carve
him up already!
[ORTE SOLDIERS]
Yes, Sir!
[ORTE SOLDIERS grunting]
--[soldiers gasp]
--Look at him!
What the hell are we up against?
The devil's smiling!
[gasps]
Where'd they come fr--?
[NOBUNAGA]
Unleash the horses!
Quickly, now! Get those
posts into place!
Hurry, dammit!
[grunts]
[NOBUNAGA]
What, are you tired?
You'll sleep when you're
a corpse! Maybe tonight!
Death is just a
matter of when!
Archers ready!
Your village meets its
end tonight, Elves.
Destroyed by your hand!
This was the home
the Orte allowed you.
Burn it to ashes and
reclaim your destiny!
Send it to hell!
The village! It's all ablaze!
[NOBUNAGA] Back in my home,
the Owari soldiers were weak.
Heh. How I'd beat my
head against the wall,
looking for any
advantage to give them.
Anything to bolster
their odds in battle.
And here I am,
stealing a page from
that monkey, Hideyoshi.
[laughs]
He builds a castle in
a day, I build a fence!
[NOBUNAGA]
Nock arrows!
[ELVES grunt]
[NOBUNAGA] All right, Elves!
Skewer the bastards!
[ORTE SOLDIERS grunting]
The Kingdom of Orte is
fighting on many fronts.
So, anyone they've sent
here can't be a soldier
who's worth half a damn.
This crowd won't
fight to the last.
They lack the discipline!
We could kill every one of them,
but there's not
much point to it.
They'll fold long before we
whittle 'em down to nothing.
We take down 20%
of their manpower,
say 40 of 'em,
they'll break like a twig.
[laughs]
[NOBUNAGA]
They don't win any glory
by killing Elves here tonight.
And if they die,
they die for naught.
Almost pity the bastards.
We don't need a rout.
All we need to do is bloody
their nose a little bit.
Ha! A fair opening gambit.
[ORTE SOLDIERS yelling]
What the hell is wrong with you?
Keep your formations tight!
That barricade is nothing!
Coordinate your attack,
and those archers will
be dead in no time!
[grunts] Commander! They covered
the arrows with shit!
What?! Wash it out!
Bathe the wound,
lest it gets infected!
But, sir, we have no water!
[VICE COMMANDER]
They contaminated their own
well too, remember?
And what little we brought
with us is almost gone.
[grunts] We've played
right into their hands.
They befouled the well in
anticipation of this moment!
The Long-Ears never
abandoned this place.
It was a trap!
They, they would
burn their homes
to the ground to
spill our blood!
Archers ready!
Fire away!
[ORTE SOLDIERS grunting]
[ORTE SOLDIER D]
How did this happen?
Come back, you cowards!
We outnumber them three
or four to one, at least!
Regroup and crush them!
[TOYOHISA yells]
[NOBUNAGA]
What the hell was that about?
That was no battle-cry.
That was like a monkey in heat!
I'm gonna take their
commander's head now.
I'm sure he's got no
objections to my plan, right?
[MALE VOICE chants]
[ORTE SOLDIERS shouting]
Someone stop him!
[yelps]
Told you so!
[gasps]
[ORTE SOLDIERS shouting]
[NOBUNAGA] Look at his eyes.
Like a bird of prey.
He found the perfect
moment to rush in,
isolate their commander,
and break the army's will
with one severed head.
Toyohisa was born to raise
havoc on the field of battle.
[ELF F]
We, we won. Didn't we?
We won!
He's right! We did it!
They ran away!
[laughs]
Victory.
[TOYOHISA]
Quiet down! We're not done!
Not with the lord
still safe in his castle!
Ya just gonna yell at it?
Or do you have an actual plan?
Not yet!
[groans]
I figured as much.
[TOYOHISA] Once you've brought
the fight to your enemy,
the only victory is absolute!
You pursue them
'til you've crushed
every last shred of resistance.
Such was the wisdom
of my father,
my uncle, their brothers,
my grandfather before them,
and my great-grandfather,
who first adopted it!
You know what you
all had in common?
Too dumb to know when to quit!
How dare you?
[chuckles] Calm that
hot blood of yours.
I have an idea for ya.
Besides, the soldiers
who ran for it, heh,
are about to be
going nowhere fast.
[ORTE SOLDIERS grunting]
[ORTE SOLDIER D]
Damn it! This is chaos!
[ORTE SOLDIERS
yelling, grunting]
The Elves! They sprung
another trap on us!
Those look covered
with shit, too.
Scheming little bastards!
[grunting]
[ORTE SOLDIER E]
Run for it!
[ORTE SOLDIER F]
No!
[YOICHI] These unsavory tactics.
Like something... he might do.
[YOICHI]
Such conduct...
It makes a mockery of bushido!
There's nothing fair about it!
[YOSHITSUNE] Bushido?
What care I for its tenets?
Fairness is a myth.
In battle, you have the
victorious and the dead.
Oh, but you are naïve, Yoichi.
What say we leave "fairness"
to the Taira and the Minamoto,
and my stupid
brothers in Kamakura?
Now silence your tongue,
dear friend.
And do exactly as I bid you.
[YOICHI]
Forget him! Do it now!
That sweet visage sheltered
the soul of a demon!
Here we go! Time for inspection!
[ORTE LORD]
Two hundred soldiers,
and no sign of them!
They haven't returned,
they haven't sent a messenger!
This should have been
the work of an hour!
I knew it!
I knew those Elves
didn't flee the village!
My lord, I do wonder
if it was prudent
to send out most
of the garrison?
Our wars rage on with
no Orte victory in sight.
For years we've held our boot
to the necks of the
conquered demi-humans.
Their anger is growing.
And we'd be fools to think
we're not courting an eruption!
Sending a few troops
at a time is folly.
We must crush this
treason with great force!
Sedition will whip
through the Elvish lands
like a plague if left unchecked.
If razing a village or
two to the ground
will break their spirits,
so be it!
If this continues, I have no
qualms about putting every one
of the Elvish women we
kidnapped to the sword.
[ORTE SOLDIER G]
Pardon, milord!
The soldiers. They've just
returned from their mission!
Ah! Capital!
They're finally back!
[NOBUNAGA] Reporting in
on milord's troops!
As regards the
subjugation force,
they've come to no
harm whatsoever!
In fact, their absence is due
to zeal for their assignment!
Requesting entry to the castle!
[wood creaks]
Now! Like we planned it.
Everyone just walk through
the gate, nice and easy.
Like you're meant to be here.
Don't spoil the surprise!
Tell me, man.
What all'd you discover?
The Long-Ears! Had they
dared to revolt?
Hmph. You could call it that.
Th-Those men are Elves
and you're a Drifter!
[NOBUNAGA]
Heh. The castle is ours.
[gasps]
How?
[TOYOHISA] Good riddance!
Hard to move in that!
[gasps]
You're going to tell me where
you're keeping the women.
The... The tower.
They're locked in the tower!
--[ORTE LORD gasps]
--[TOYOHISA] Follow me!
But... all my soldiers.
What happened?
Where are all my men?
[NOBUNAGA] Ah, yes.
Those poor unfortunates.
You shouldn't have asked.
Most are slain.
And the rest are being hunted
down in the woods as we speak.
But, try not to fret.
You'll be with them soon enough.
Mixed with dirt, shit n' their
corpses amid my saltpeter mound,
awaiting reincarnation
into a more noble form
as fine gunpowder!
[laughs]
[ORTE SOLDIER H]
Stay back!
[ORTE SOLDIER I gasps]
I surrender!
Please, I give up!
Damn you!
[gasps]
What? Why not?
He no longer holds a blade.
You slay your foe
with weapon in hand.
Not while he begs for mercy!
But they've...
murdered so many of--
[TOYOHISA]
Act with honor!
[gasps]
[TOYOHISA] Lest you forget,
we're here to rescue the women.
Ready?
[grunts]
Let's go.
Right.
[ORTE SOLDIER J]
Huh? Who's there?
[ELVES pant, gasp]
[TOYOHISA growls]
I was wrong to speak of mercy.
All the men within
this fortress...
...are a disease!
[TOYOHISA] I will carve them up,
spill their foul blood,
and reduce their villainy
to so much steaming meat!
[MALE VOICE chants]