Can you see them?
No, sir.
There's no sign of them yet.
But I can feel them.
It could happen any time.
[CARNEADES SOLDIER A
speaking Orte]
[CARNEADES SOLDIER B
[speaking Orte]
[CARNEADES SOLDIERS laughing]
[HARUAKIRA]
It's the laughter of dead men.
They won't last two days.
[HARUAKIRA] Act as my proxy.
I am needed elsewhere.
[OCTOBRIST B]
You speak of the old men?
[HARUAKIRA]
Indeed.
Without them at the army's helm,
this land will fall.
[HARUAKIRA]
If we are to survive this,
Drifters and soldiers
alike must fight as one!
[CARNEADES CHIEF OF STAFF
speaking Orte]
[speaking Orte]
[CARNEADES CHIEF OF STAFF
speaking Orte]
[speaking Orte]
[SCIPIO, HANNIBAL groan]
Tell me, boy, what're
you two arguing about?
We'd prefer that he relinquish
command to you and your rival.
Huh?! When were ya gonna
ask my opinion on this?
I know it's a tall order.
But our men will die
without you at the helm.
Really? If they cannot
soorvive by their own wits,
maybe they're meant
for the underworld.
[CARNEADES SOLDIERS
speaking Orte]
[SCIPIO]
I need no knowledge
of a tongue to perceive
when its words are petty.
[HANNIBAL]
Ho! Scipio!
Eh?
[HANNIBAL groans]
I'm about to pee!
Huh?
Don't you dare piss yourself.
They're already
speaking ill of us!
Would that I could hold it!
Old age makes a tyrant
of every bladder!
I am undone, Scipio!
Ah...
Gods, how I tire of this
piddling Carthaginian.
[ALL laughing]
[HANNIBAL growls]
[HANNIBAL chuckles]
They laugh...
These callow youth who
never saw me in my prime.
[laughing continues]
[CARNEADES CHIEF OF STAFF
speaking Orte]
[SCIPIO growls]
Huh?
[gasps]
[speaking Orte]
[SCIPIO]
That old man on the floor?
He could rout a
million of your soldiers,
and be none the worse for it!
That man... is a Titan!
You are in the
presence of Hannibal!
Hannibal of  Carthage!
When the standard of
the Roman Empire
flew over much of
the known world,
this man gave us cause
to tremble like no other!
[speaking Orte]
Damn you!
[HARUAKIRA]
That's enough. Let him go.
[SCIPIO grunts]
[HARUAKIRA]
The die has been cast.
We must prepare to
make our retreat.
Octobrist and Drifter
alike must flee.
This place will be enveloped
in the coming carnage.
The Black King's denizens
are thirsty for blood.
So before the fighting begins,
the Drifters must be
ushered to safety,
no matter how high the cost.
Scipio...
You honor me.
[SCIPIO grunts]
Well you did come out on top
at the Battle of Cannae,
even though I carried the
day when it mattered most!
[HANNIBAL grunts]
What did you just say,
you tactical plagiarist?
I'ma gonna scatter your teeth!
[HANNIBAL]
Dirty thieving Roman!
[OLMINU]
This is Olmine, sir.
Do you copy?
What's the situation there--
[static buzzes]
[gasps]
[OCTOBRIST D]
They're dampening it.
Then the hour has come!
[CARNEADES SOLDIERS
speaking Orte]
[BUTCH] Got any clue
what the ruckus is about?
Can't really say that I do.
Spare me a coffin-nail?
Ain't got a-one to my name.
Done smoked the last of 'em.
[BUTCH] Bullshit. You got
a pair of 'em hid away on ya.
Right miserly, after getting
us stuck out here.
[KID] Callin' names ain't
gonna net you no tobacco.
[groans]
Lord love a duck.
[BUTCH] They keep
tomorrows in a vault
we ain't never learned to crack.
All men like us get
is today, Sundance.
Sure does make a fella long
for the creature comforts.
[CARNEADES SOLDIER C
speaking Orte]
[OWL]
Crusade! Crusade!
His Majesty the
Black King approaches!
Crusade! Crusade!
Ye know neither the
day nor the hour!
Crusade! Crusade!
Those who have ears, take heed!
Those who have eyes, witness!
Those who have mouths, profess!
Know that the King is here!
Crusade! Crusade! Crusade!
Humanity's eradication
begins here and now!
Serve him with zeal,
ye slayers of men!
Give yourselves over to
the will of the Black King!
Surrender yourselves,
body and soul!
Lo, the Black King.
High Lord of all the Ends.
We are too late!
He's taken the field!
[growls]
Is your hatred so complete?
Towards the Drifters?
And this world?
And all else?
[speaking Orte]
[BLACK KING]
End them.
[MALE VOICE shouts]
[CARNEADES SOLDIER D
speaking Orte]
[ENDS SOLDIERS
grunting, yelling]
[BLACK KING]
Hijikata.
Joan of Arc.
[BLACK KING] Anastasia
Nikolaevna Romanova.
Serve thy needs.
[YOSHITSUNE] Finally, you let
them off the leash.
Do you really mean to
seal this world's doom?
[BLACK KING]
You pledge me no fealty.
Indeed. For such
freedom is a boon to me.
I beg your indulgence
to continue thus.
[BLACK KING]
Which side are you on,
Minamoto no Yoshitsune?
The Drifters, or the Ends?
[YOSHITSUNE chuckles]
It's hard to say.
Whichever one
piques my interest!
[CARNEADES SOLDIER D
speaking Orte]
[CARNEADES SOLDIER E
[ENDS AIR SUPPORT A
speaking Orte]
[ENDS SOLDIERS grunting]
[CARNEADES SOLDIER E
speaking Orte]
[ENDS AIR SUPPORT A
[ENDS SOLDIER A speaking Orte]
[screams]
[ENDS GOBLIN grunting]
[ENDS AIR SUPPORT A
speaking Orte]
We can do nothing for them.
These men are dead.
But what about
the Drifters here?
[gasps]
Friend or foe? I can't tell!
Which are you?
Which one?
[NAOSHI]
What the hell is this bullshit?
Fuckin' fuck!
I don't recognize any of this!
Hey, no one said you could
sleep on the job, you asshole!
Get that engine running
right the fuck now!
[engine revs]
[NAOSHI] Fucking thank you!
That's more like it!
[ENDS SOLDIERS shouting]
[NAOSHI]
Wait a fuckin' second!
Now that I'm looking at it,
I don't recognize a goddamn
inch of this terrain!
Can somebody tell me what
the hell I'm flying over?
[gasp]
The fuck?
[AIR ENDS A gasps]
Fuck. Really? A dragon?
What the shit?
The son-a-bitchin'
things don't even exist!
But there you are,
clogging up the sky
next to me with that
big scaly bastard!
Sir! Which side is he on?
I haven't a clue!
For now, focus on
rescuing the Drift--!
[BOTH gasp]
[ALL gasp]
[ALL gasping]
[screams]
[CARNEADES SOLDIER F
speaking Orte]
[speaking Orte]
[gasps]
[JOAN OF ARC]
Je suis. Je suis en feu.
The burning-- This is hell!
Unfair that I burn alone!
Join me.
Let me burn you to ash!
Smoldering heaps of ash
that will fly on the wind!
[laughs]
Yes! Magnifique!
Let the inferno run riot
over man and God alike!
[BOTH gasp]
[speaking Orte]
Slumber for all of time.
[MAN speaking Orte]
[ENDS SOLDIER growls]
[CARNEADES MOTHER pants]
[growls]
[TOWNSPEOPLE shouting]
[NAOSHI gasps]
[gasping continues]
You bastard!
So firebombing people is
how you wanna play this?
[speaking Orte]
[JOAN OF ARC]
Shall I warm it for you?
[ALL gasp]
[chuckles]
[speaking Orte]
[CARNEADES SOLDIERS yelling]
[gasps]
[laughs]
[BOTH yell]
[JOAN OF ARC laughs]
[KID] No sign of 'em.
This ain't looking good.
Naw, it ain't. Whaddya say?
Do we wait, or cut an' run?
[KAFET]
To the wagon! Please, hurry!
--[BUTCH] Nuts.
--[KAFET] Quickly, both of you!
With any luck,
we'll catch up later!
Now go! Make haste!
[BUTCH]
Haulin' antiques today.
Sorry, I didn't quite
make that out.
[BUTCH exhales]
[HANNIBAL grunts]
Dressed funny, aintcha?
Oh, and you're not?
[HARUAKIRA] We've done
all that we can here.
[BOTH]
Hm?
The Northern Wall has fallen,
and the Kingdom of Carneades
has met its doom.
Scipio... Hannibal... We ask
much of you to strategize
so soon after your
journey to our realm!
But, please.
Help us, if you can.
Do we have a chance?
Any chance of defeating
the Black King?
Or has our fate been sealed?
Hard to say.
Whassa your take on it?
[HANNIBAL chuckles]
Half a chance, at least.
[HARUAKIRA]
Hm. That's enough for me!
If the Drifters in the woods
join up with these men,
what a force they'll make!
With warriors of that caliber,
the righteous may prevail.
Get them out of here!
[ENDS SOLDIER A speaking Orte]
[ENDS SOLDIERS grunting]
[BUTCH] Attaboy, Sundance!
Keep perforatin' these bastards!
Happy t'oblige, but I'm
running low on munitions!
What is that wondrous device?
With that thing, I'd have
Rome whimpering at my feet!
Always with the gimmicks!
[BUTCH]
Hold onto yer fundaments!
Gotta smoke, friend?
[ENDS SOLDIER C gasps]
[BUTCH]
Go bum me one off the Devil!
Yeehaw!
We're nearing the
West Gate! Hurry up!
[BUTCH gasps]
[BUTCH grunts]
[roars]
Target down! I tore
that dragon a new asshole!
[NAOSHI laughs]
Now, for the rest of 'em!
There's a flock of those
bastards at my twelve!
Chalk 'em up to Noushi Kanno,
Commander of the 301st
"Shinsen-gumi" Squadron!
[AIR ENDS 3B yells]
Look at you, flapping those
wings like you own the sky!
That distinction belongs to me!
I don't know what the
fuck is going on here,
but as long as I got ammo,
that's good enough!
[HARUAKIRA]
A Drifter!
He's one of ours!
I'll never let you
get away with this.
Not while I live!
The evil you have wrought here,
you will pay for it, Black King!
I swear you will pay!
[ENDS GOBLIN B grunts]
[BLACK KING] The humans
are fruit... of a curséd tree.
[caws]
[BLACK KING]
Chase them.
Seek them.
Find them.
Kill them!
The Drifters cannot
be suffered to live.
Their blood must
be spilled, one and all!
I, the Inexorable Tribulation,
have thus decreed.
[OLMINU]
What a horrible time
to lose contact with
the Grand Master.
Ah! What do I do?
The Northern Wall
couldn't have been breached
tonight, could it have?
Don't worry about that.
You've got enough on your
plate with these three.
Oh, what do I do?
[OLMINU gasps]
[ALL yell]
[whimpers]
I know you've been watching us
from afar, but on whose orders?
[yelps]
[OLMINU] No! He's gonna
cut my head off!
He's one of those ghosts
who loves to take 'em!
[TOYOHISA]
Who're you calling a ghost?
[OLMINU grunts]
Some sort of spy, perhaps?
Eh, she seems too
dumb for that.
I'd wager not.
Hey, Toyohisa.
Go on.
Notice she spoke our tongue
before ya knocked her out?
Really?!
Pretty sure.
You'd better tell me
everything I want to know!
What are you waiting for?!
[yells]
Please! Spare me!
I don't know what you
wanna know, honest!
Then maybe you prefer
he drag it out of you.
Greetings! Demon King
of the Sixth Heaven!
I'm a big fan of
wholesale slaughter
and relaxing with a drink
served in the skull of my foe!
[screams]
My, my name is Olmine,
and I'm one of the magicians
working for the
Octobrist Organization!
The Grand Master gave me orders
to keep an eye on you Drifters,
otherwise I never would
have dared to spy on you
and I'm very sorry about it!
[groans]
What is she going on about?
Say it again, and make
it simpler this time.
The guy in red is
kind of a dummy.
That wasn't complex!
Who are you calling a dummy?!
I've beheaded men for less!
Oh, fine then.
You're not a dummy.
Does that make
you feel any better?
Okay. I'll try to
simplify it for you.
In this realm, those of you
who hail from the other world
are known as Drifters.
Like I was telling you before,
I'm a member of the
Octobrist Organization,
a group tasked with
monitoring the activities
of people like you and
bringing them together.
You were sent here to
battle other travelers
from your world. Those of
evil intent, known as Ends.
Ask if!
That story is such bullshit!
No way!
[shouts]
[MALE VOICE chants]