[hooves clatter]
That's quite far enough!
[ORTE SOLDIER A]
Who goes there?
[ORTE SOLDIER B]
Whose carriages are these?
[ALLISTER] They belong
to Count Saint-Germain,
leading light of the Empire.
Was the banner too obtuse?
It's a brave man
who bars his entry.
Yes, but, so many
carriages at once?
No one gave us any warning.
This isn't how things
are done here, Milord.
Your name. I would have it.
[gasps]
[ALLISTER] You had the gall to
impede the Count's cavalcade.
I daresay the front lines could
benefit from your audacity.
What is your name, Sir?
Please, go right on ahead.
[ALLISTER chuckles]
Wise choice.
These are turbulent times.
And my master can no longer
watch the war effort unfold
from the safety of afar.
The count and his convoy
behind us will join the fight.
All for the glory
of the Orte Empire!
Any help would be a boon!
Um... Raise the gate already!
Hurry up!
[ALLISTER] Past the guards,
and not one lie uttered.
My contessa will indeed
be joining the fight.
I simply neglected to
tell them for which side.
[SHARA grunts]
I'm burning up in here.
[ELF A]
And the stench!
We're all going to die
amid this horrible smell.
Shut up, ya squealing piglet!
At least we don't
stink like a forge!
Quiet, you! You're the
one that reek!
Whoever insists on
touching my butt,
had better stop it at once!
Aw! And now they got a boob!
Well, I know it's not me!
[OLMINE] Lying bastard!
When have you not!
[NOBUNAGA] Prove it, then!
Trace the hand up to my arm an--
Shut up!
So this is the city
of Verlina, Orte's capital.
What a desolate place.
[NOBUNAGA]
True enough, But still...
...we should make it the seat
of our government, as well.
[TOYOHISA] Not much of a seat.
The buildings are sound enough,
but I've seen carrion
with more life to it.
[NOBUNAGA]
Me too.
These stall on the main road
into town should be brimming
with goods, but instead they
hawk scraps. Trade is dead.
Every civillian I
see is an old one
and the streets are
more deserted than not.
They threw their able
bodied into the war effort.
Place is on it's
on its last legs.
Hell, we're doing them
a favor by conquering it.
Half-tempted to burn it all.
Look at this place.
At this point, cutting off its
head would be a kindness.
Bring its suffering to an end.
[TOYOHISA]
"Coo day ta"?
What the hell
does that mean?
You cover your words
with greasepaint, too.
Silence, rustic.
It's the artful seizing of
a capital from the inside.
I'll lead the whole
sordid affair
and by the time
our fun is over,
Orte will belong to you.
Remind me again which one
of you's in charge?
I don't remember
asking for the job,
but they gave it to
me all the same.
Tell me, lad.
What are your names,
the three of you?
We are all Drifters here.
As such, you might
be familiar to me.
Toyohisa, loyal son
of the Shimazu clan!
Shimazu Toyohisa. Hm...
Ah! The Battle of
Sekigahara in 1600.
I'm Nasu no Yoichi.
Oh, I know you!
The archer from the Genpei War.
Your exploits have endured.
And you are?
Oda Nobunaga!
You're the most
famous of all!
[NOBUNAGA laughs] Course I am!
How could I not be?
[SAINT GERMI]
Who's the relic over there?
[NOBUNAGA] Damned if I know.
Some raspberry addict?
[NOBUNAGA]
Since you've heard of us,
I assume you hail
from a point in history
long after any of ours.
[SAINT GERMI laughs]
Care to hear what happened
to the Shimazu after Sekigahara?
I'm a veritable
fount of knowledge.
You could tell me, but it
would be a waste of breath.
My uncle fled.
That's why I stayed behind,
to buy him time enough to quit
the field and escape.
If he made it
back to Satsuma,
I know well what
happened after that!
The Shimazu destroyed
the Tokugawa.
Whether it took us
one year or a hundred,
I know that the final
victory was ours to be had.
[gasps]
To say such a thing.
To predict such an outcome
after the bloodletting
your forces had to endure.
This boy has audacity in spades!
Yeah. What you said.
Sorry about that.
He's a mouthy one.
Forget him!
Do me instead!
What do people say about
me in the future, huh?
Japan remembers
you in curious ways.
They think you could fly!
Shoot lasers out
of your very eyes.
What the hell's a laser?
[SAINT GERMI]
Brought hell to earth!
And made green tea
out of your own body.
They know you for
being a good archer.
Okay, then?
[BOTH] What the hell kind
of world are you from?
[NOBUNAGA]
It's a shame.
I'd like to go into this
fight much better prepared.
More muskets made,
for one thing.
And more time for teaching
the troops how to use them.
That cherry blossom of a count
rushed the timeline
too damn much.
[TOYOHISA]
Eh. Life is a river.
Why resist the flow?
Much better to let it
take us where it will.
[NOBUNAGA] Spoken like one
who's never been dashed
agaisnt the rocks or
drowned within the rapids.
[TOYOHISA] Life or death,
I could care less.
[NOBUNAGA] I prefer life,
thank you very much.
[TOYOHISA] Why do you
trust that growling geisha?
He's a snake.
[NOBUNAGA]
Indeed.
But a traitor's mind
is no great riddle.
Betrayal's in their blood.
As soon as it suits their needs,
they'll stick a
knife in your back.
However, they do it
to profit in some way.
It's not based on anything
so tawdry as emotion.
No, not that old viper.
If he's screwing
over someone else,
he's too busy right
now to screw us over!
[TOYOHISA] I don't know
what to make of them.
The count and his entourage
are rather peculiar.
[NOBUNAGA]
"Peculiar"? That's diplomatic!
I'd have gone with
garish or outlandish!
Yeah! Outlandish is a good one!
You know I can hear you, right?!
Shut your mouth, you ingrate!
[ARISTOCRAT A]
Count Saint-Germain.
While it lay within your power
to summon us all hence,
I cannot help but wonder,
why now? When the health of
the empire has almost ebbed
beyond the physic's care?
[SAINT GERMI]
Speaking of that...
...the Orte you serve
no longer exists.
[ARISTOCRATS gasp]
Long ago, Father and I
tapped into the power
of the people's discontent.
For 50 years,
the seams held fast.
But its knell has rung.
I'm afraid I'm calling
the grand experiment off.
I think you'll agree Orte's
had a good run of it,
all things considered.
Such is the fate of
an empire, given time.
Lest you fret too
heartily over this,
know that the Drifter
Toyohisa will lead
our people into a new
dawn of prosperity.
As for this august body,
I thank you for your years of
service and bid you all adieu.
What are you saying?
If it's meant in jest,
it misses the mark!
Was I unclear?
I thought I explained myself
in simple language.
Perhaps you are an idiot.
I must confess,
that accounts for a lot.
Guards! Make haste!
The Count gives voice
to treason! Take him!
You can yell at that
doorway all you like.
They're not coming, you dolt!
Would that you could share
in the guardsmen's fate!
You villain!
To act the ally
and author a coup!
Father would do the
same thing, were he here.
But he's not.
Who is in favor of
this housecleaning?
Speak!
I support the Count
in this action.
You're not alone.
I have no objection.
Wha-- all of you?
[SAINT GERMI chuckles]
Do you think I'd
convene such a meeting
without laying
the groundwork?
You simpleton.
You two, sitting like
lumps over there.
Come! Pledge me
your support already!
[BOTH]
I agree with the dissolution
of Orte's government.
[SAINT GERMI]
Mm-hm. Very good.
[ARISTOCRAT B]
However...
Go on!
I must oppose any plan in
which we hand the country
over to Drifter scum.
[ARISTOCRAT B]
Only the Black King
can lead Orte to
greatness once again.
We throw ourselves
at his feet,
and we pray that he
takes mercy upon us all.
We will be his vanguard,
and through the destruction
of the human race,
we will earn his favor.
Vile Rasputin! Release that man!
Count Saint-Germain.
Both of us want to
take over Orte, da?
But only you will try it
looking like a harlot.
[BOTH] You're in for
a rude awakening
if you think I'll
let you win here!
[grunts]
[chuckles]
[SAINT GERMI gasps]
[RASPUTIN]
Hm?
[NOBUNAGA]
Now I've seen it all.
So who's the ghost, and why's
he getting in the way?
So you are the Drifters
I hear so much about.
Hard to believe
you defeated both
Joan and Gilles de Rais.
I am the mystic, Rasputin.
I hope it is not too
hurtful to your pride,
but the Black Lord is too busy
to stamp out vermin
such as you.
[MALE VOICE chants]
[RASPUTIN] Orchestrating
the end of the world
takes a goodly amount of time.
How I hope you enjoy
this little surprise.
[BOTH gasp]
Mercy!
[ARISTOCRAT D]
Our capitol is ablaze!
Our troops are pouring into
the capital as we speak.
[SAINT GERMI grunts]
[chuckles] Ah. I do
apologize for this.
Defeat on the cusp of
victory is a bitter pill.
[KOBOLDS]
Huh?
[KOBOLDS grunting]
[gasps]
[gasping]
[NOBUNAGA]
That shut 'em up.
You must be their leader.
Shimazu Toyohisa,
of Japan's Sengoku era.
Look at the mess you made in
the blink of an eye, no less.
You are no stranger
to savagery, my friend.
Of course, I knew
that with how badly
you concussed our dear Joan.
You really should have killed
her when you had the chance.
[ARISTOCRAT B grunts]
[NOBUNAGA]
Oh... That has to sting.
I know we're on
opposite sides and all,
but I feel for the poor bastard.
Right when he was about
to lord his genius
over us from afar,
Toyohisa ignores him,
and stomps his minion instead.
Damn good way to
take him down a peg.
The lad operates
on instinct.
It's not that he can't
read a situation.
He just refuses to.
I wonder if it's a trait they
pushed on him as a boy,
or just inborn
Satsuma bravado.
It's his strongest weapon
and his greatest weakness,
both at once.
Liable to get him killed
if he's not careful.
Toyohisa, that's quite enough.
Killing him does us no good.
[gasps]
You're looking a little
green around the gills
all of a sudden.
[gasps]
[NOBUNAGA] What's wrong?
You were smug a moment ago.
I thought you wanted to gloat.
Guess the cat's got your tongue.
Suddenly you've got nothing
to say. What a shame.
I came here knowing
full well there'd be a fight.
I'll kill anyone who
stands in our way.
Come, and I'll paint the
streets red with your blood!
Something tells me
our friend here
wanted to take this
place by stealth.
That sour look of yours doesn't
change the fact we're here.
Even that painted nightmare
of a count is looking prettier
than you are!
Whether you know it or not,
you've done us a real favor.
We Drifters have to save Orte
from the threat
of the Ends now.
Just like that,
you've legitimized our coup.
Much obliged!
My goodness!
If looks could kill!
You were so pleased
a moment ago!
What could've changed?
C'mon, where's that smile?
[growls]
Guess I'll see you on
the battlefield, then.
[RASPUTIN growls]
Nyet! Damn it!
Bastards! How dare they?
[HIJIKATA] What of
your progress, Rasputin?
Speak.
They've come, Hijikata!
Drifters are in Verlina!
I preyed upon its leaders.
Our forces marched
there in haste.
The Drifters never
should have been there.
And still they set
my plans awry!
How does one prepare
for such chaos?
Their's are the strategies
of fools and madmen!
I cannot predict the course
of a ship in a hurricane!
No one can!
[HIJIKATA] Calm yourself, monk.
Such is the nature of war.
We strive towards an outcome,
but nothing is certain.
Only the shedding of blood.
Leave it to me.
I will conquer Orte.
I will not allow the Drifters
to mar our plans in any way.
[BLACK KING]
Hijikata.
[HIJIKATA gasps]
[BLACK KING]
Rasputin.
[RASPUTIN gasps]
[BLACK KING] If you cannot
dislodge them from the capital,
I give you leave to
pursue a darker path;
Verlina's destruction.
If it will not be ours,
it will know the
fullness of our wrath.
Rain fire and death upon them,
and let both eat their fill.
The Drifters will
gain nothing by this,
but the hard-fought
lordship of a charnel house.
Lord.
Thy will be done,
my glorious ebon king!
[BLACK KING] Whether we
conquerit now or later,
their fate is set.
We shall suffer none to live.
[NOBUNAGA] Enough sleep,
you idiots, wake up!
[gasping]
What did I... What did I do?
Don't play the fool with me,
you piece of shit!
The Black King's army.
You let them into town.
How many, huh?
How many of them are there?
I-I dunno. What are
you getting at?
Who are you?
Why do you yell at me?
What'd I'd do?
I don't remember any--
[groans]
He's not above using pain
to wrap up a conversation.
This is my shocked face.
Bring me a map of
the town at once!
Hurry up, dammit!
I laid it on a bit too thick.
If I lose after
all that mockery,
the Count'll never
let me forget it.
That's the coldest treatment
Rasputin's gotten
since they tossed
him in the river.
[NOBUNAGA] Two hundred Elves,
two hundred Dwarves.
And no idea what
we're facing off against.
We're lucky your carriages
held that many.
Plus their armor and weapons.
The fighting men I stationed
beyond the capital should be
heading here as we speak.
Every one is a warrior
of high renown.
And we have a full 500.
Five hundred?
This is war, not a tea ceremony!
We thought we'd be fighting
the hapless city guards!
Not the Ends!
Besides, that 500
is my whole army!
What?! That's your army?!
Ha! And again, ha!
What kind of Orte big-wig
has only 500 soldiers
at their disposal?!
I prize quality over quantity!
Any two-bit despot could fill
the ranks with slugabeds!
Sorry to interrupt,
but your army is here!
Already?
They're quite--
Quite what?
[NOBUNAGA] No doubt
they're ready for battle.
But, I'm not sure why every
one of them's bare-chested?
Uh. I have a theory about that.
Hey. Real talk.
Your army's morale,
it's high, yeah?
High? Puh-lease!
Behold the Sacred
Band of Thebes!
They just happened to be the
most perfect specimens
of manhood I could find!
My motives were pure, dammit!
Now I understand why there's
only 500 members in his army!
Of course!
Everyone had to enlist
with their best friend!
Oh yeah! You nailed it,
all right! Numbskull.
Thebai Hieros Lokhos.
Wait, so you've heard of
them before? Who are you, man?
Epaminondas, oblique phalanxes!
Two-bit thief! You stole that
stratagem from Gorgidas!
Who is this geezer? I don't
like how he's yelling at me!
Don't know!
The Octobrists said he's
Hannibal something-or-other.
The Hannibal?
I need to eat something.
Rome sounds tasty.
[SAINT GERMI gasps] May I die
before I get that old!
[inhales]
At the ready!
All right,
you Sacred Band of Thebes,
present your weaponry!
Over the past week, we've
had them running drills
with sticks in
lieu of the rifles.
Either way, this will
be something to see.
[NOBUNAGA chuckles]
[TOYOHISA]
Good so far.
[NOBUNAGA]
They look like guns,
but they're nothing
until they fire.
[YOICHI] Muskets.
A sobering sight indeed.
[SAINT GERMI]
Am I dreaming?
Such glorious weapons, in the
hands of my private army!
[THEBAN A] So this is a
real gun. I feel ill-at-ease.
Day n' night we worked
to get these made.
Hundred ain't enough to arm
all of 'em, but these'll do.
Before you go
thinking we're idle,
take a look at this beauty.
Should serve ya
fair-to-middlin'.
[TOYOHISA gasps]
[MALE VOICE chants]
What do ya think?
[chuckles]
[BOTH laugh]
They're laughing.
Why are they both laughing?
Just smile and nod
and we'll all be okay.
[TOYOHISA] Nobunaga will
lead the musketeers,
and keep them in formation.
Dwarves, I'll be fighting
alongside you. Hand-to-hand.
Yoichi will take the
Elvish contingent.
May your aim be true.
We'll lure them in and cut
them down. No one escapes.
They're corpses the
moment they take the field.
[NOBUNAGA] Look at that
glint in Toyohisa's eye.
Like a hawk surveying the field.
He lives for war.
Well, we don't need to
put every one of them
to the sword, right?
Once they see the
capital is denied them,
they'll beat a hasty
retreat soon after.
We kill them all.
I don't care how fast they run.
They're done for!
Y'know, for a man of letters,
you're no good at strategy.
[SAINT GERMI]
What?! How dare you, sir?!
[NOBUNAGA] If I were them,
I'd switch to another plan
the moment I figured out this
place isn't up for grabs.
Instead of conquest,
one of destruction.
Pillaging homes at will.
Kidnapping. Even murder.
Now the peasants are the target.
I would leave all manner of
hell for them in my wake.
Casualties would be high.
We're wise to their puppetry
of the aristocrats from afar.
They do the Ends no good now.
If the Black King wants to
end the world, why sack a town?
[SAINT GERMI chuckles]
[NOBUNAGA] The place is sure to
suffer under their lack of rule.
Ideally, we'd let them
attack for a bit,
then rescue the Orte and take
the reins as their saviors.
Oh well.
Their lives are forfeit!
All of them!
We offer no quarter!
Now, men! Are you with me?!
[ALL cheer]
Tell me true, are we
ready for this Yoichi?
We'll be fighting the
Black Kings monsters.
Not within our homeland,
but in the heart of Orte.
How could you not be ready?
If you ever doubt yoursefl,
yell out "Minamoto Banzai"!
Still no idead what that means,
but, "Minamoto Banzai."
[NOBUNAGA] My victory in
Nagashino was a thing of beauty!
Now I've got men that
don't know how to shoot!
Where did my life go wrong?!
Care to inspect
the troops, milord?
I second that.
I'm going to kill
you twice, Mitsuhide!
[ALL gasp]
Olmine! Can you hear me?
You're on message duty
between the spheres!
Copy that! I'll relay
the messages!
Never done anything of
the sort, but I'll try.
They're coming. Mark them.
They're coming.
Right for us. Like clockwork.
[TOYOHISA]
Come on.
Come on. Come on!
Come on!
[NOBUNAGA]
Thebans, at the ready!
Form a line!
This world has never
known gunfire.
Combat will never be the same!
You are harbingers of a new era!
From these 100 guns,
millions are sure to follow!
Your deeds tonight will change
the course of history!
Not yet, Thebans. Not yet!
Wait for your prey.
Let them come.
Let them seal their fate.
Closer!
Hold, damn you.
Open fire!
[KOBOLDS grunting]
[THEBANS gasp]
Heh!
[NOBUNAGA] Factoring the
destruction of the shot itself,
plus the spectacle of it,
even in the hands
of a rank amateur,
the effect of this
new weapon...
[gunshots]
[NOBUNAGA]
...it's powerful!
It's transcendent!
Signal Yoichi! Do you
hear me, Olmine?
[gasps]
Yo-Yoichi!
[YOICHI]
That is incredible.
But I prefer our way.
It's time to join the fight.
Aim for the center of
them and rain death!
[gasps]
[KOBOLDS grunting]
[NOBUNAGA] Perfectly executed!
These spheres are incredible!
What I wouldn't give to
revisit my past battles
with a few of these in tow!
[THEBAN B grunts]
[THEBANS grunting]
[growls]
[NOBUNAGA] They're slow,
and who wouldn't be?
One more volley and
this battle is over.
But the men are
nervous enough already.
[NOBUNAGA] Don't rush!
Measure your gunpowder well!
[NOBUNAGA]
Nothing is more important!
Second volley!
[NOBUNAGA]
Fire!
[KOBOLDS grunting]
[NOBUNAGA]
The true value of a musket
isn't the distance or
force of its shot,
but the fear it
leaves in its wake!
Every new bullet is born
of thunder and smoke!
The corpses pile higher!
And soon, their bravery
has left them.
Soon they can go no further.
They're afraid...
...and neither love nor duty
will spur them forward again!
Kill 'em all!
[NOBUNAGA] Our warriors carve
into the foe without mercy.
[MURASAKI] The human musketeers,
led by the wily Nobunaga.
The Elven archers, led by
the peerless Yoichi.
[DWARVES shouting]
[KOBOLDS gasp]
[MURASAKI]
And last...
...the Dwarven infantrymen,
led by the devilish Shimazu.
That's the best
possible outcome.
[HIJIKATA]
Shimazu...
You will die by my hand!
[MALE VOICE chants]