Stella:
Ikki and I...
have become lovers.
But it's been... two weeks,
and he hasn't done anything!
(sighs)
You idiot...
Mangetsu:
Five for five!
Victorious yet again:
Ikki Kurogane!
The freshman falls!
Dominated by "The Worst One."
A moniker that just won't do
anymore folks!
"Another One,"
the King of the Ring!
He is just... extraordinary!
Ikki:
What?
You wanna learn
swordsmanship from me?
Oh yes!
You are the strongest
swordsman in the class!
Since we have someone
like you around...
Kagami:
We'd be crazy not
to take advantage of it!
Uhh... Ahhhh...
Mmm... Hmph!
Oh! Well I guess...
Ikki:
Okay... If I can be
useful to you, then I
don't mind teaching you.
Oh, awesome!
"An exclusive!
The Invincible Another One..."
"Practicing in Paradise
with Hagun's Ikki Kurogane!"
Kagami:
That'll be
my next front page!
I see,
so that's why...
Don't even
worry about it!
Okay so we can start
tomorrow‐ right?
Thank you very much!
Mmm...
Male Student 1:
Why do all the girls
think he's so awesome?
Look at him‐ man...
Don't get too proud of
yourself... F‐knight reject.
Hi everyone. Let's go ahead
and get started...
Today's final...
Bleeeeegh...
No!
Whoa! Miss Yuri!
You're too generous‐
you know.
Hm?
Every one of those girls
is a talented blazer‐ too.
If you're going to teach them,
you're only creating
future competition
for yourself.
Yeah! I'd love
nothing more.
Really?
If that's to
be the case...
then I say it's
worth training them.
Besides... bad things
can happen to them as well.
Ikki:
When they find themselves
in some kind of trouble...
if there's a chance
that my advice may be able
to help them...
Then I'll do
whatever I can.
Like I said, you're
way too generous.
You might be right.
(gasps)
Hmph!
Stella?
I‐It's nothing.
Really? Okay, then.
Uh, actually... it's been
2 weeks since we started
dating each other, right?
I thought maybe...
it's about time to...
do something...
you know...
like lovers do?
You know‐ because
you and I are...
(snoring)
Mmmm!
Ikki:
You're doing great.
Hang on for 30 more seconds!
Y‐Yes!
Ikki sir? What exactly is this
training supposed to improve?
Balance... use of
your inner muscles...
...and the importance
of your core strength.
When you're
in a fight...
you'll most often be putting
your weight on one leg‐
not both.
Ikki:
The Chinese Masters...
used to call this the "error
of double pressure."
If you stand with equal pressure
on both sides‐ you're stuck.
Oh I see now!
I mean‐ I don't
know what it means,
but I'm writing it
down word for word!
Well, that's, uh...
You look like you're having
an awful lot of fun‐
surrounded by
girls...
You worthless
failed knight.
This is
bullshit man!
You're not
fooling any of us!
Who are you?
Students:
(chattering at commotion)
Heh, heh.
What do you guys
think you're doing?!
Isn't it obvious?
We're gonna put this loser...
back in his place!
(battle cry)
Ikki no!
Damn you!
(struggling)
(gun jamming)
Shit! What the fuck?!
Ah!
(whimpers)
Uhh... ah...
Deploying your device
in an undesignated area...
is against school rules.
We're sorry, Sir!
Huh?
What lame bad guys!
You should say:
"We'll get you next time!"
and then laugh maniacally
as you run away!
Don't you guys
watch any movies?!
Well... would that
actually be a good thing?
We're sorry! We were just
so envious of you sir!
You're so
strong man!
And all the
girls like you!
I wanna be
strong like you!
I want girls
to like me!
Will you please teach
us too‐ Mr. Kurogane?
Please!
(annoyed sign)
You guys are really
crappy bullies...
Of course I will!
Stand up and balance on one foot
like everyone else...
Huh?
Master! As you command!
Really? Master...?
Extraordinary!
Even the worst bullies
are immediately reformed.
This is the revolutionary
Kurogane Method!
I'll bet I could make big money
if I sold this online.
Heh.
Female Student:
E‐excuse me...?
We know you're busy‐
Master Kurogane,
but could you
teach us too?
Mmm‐hmm!
Please join us!
Stella:
Your "class" is getting
really big, Ikki.
Ikki:
Yeah, I guess it is...
But unlike me‐ they all have
seriously formidable abilities.
If I can help improve
their swordsmanship,
even just a little,
they'll all be very powerful.
Hey, Ikki?
Aren't you thirsty?
Actually,
yeah I am.
Are you?
Okay then...
Shizuku:
Big Brother!
Ikki:
Shizuku!
Aren't you such
a lucky guy?
Your very loving and
devoted little sister
brought you
something to drink!
Here you go,
Big Brother!
Thank you.
That was nice.
Huh?
So how is it?
Do you think it
tastes like me?
Huh?!
I'm only kidding...
It's not like I put my mouth
on that drink or anything.
No‐ I definitely didn't...
That is a weirdly
specific joke...
But more
importantly...
Stella is standing there with
her mouth hanging half‐open....
Why do you have two bottles
behind your back Princess?
Huh? It's only because
I'm extremely thirsty!
I'm going to drink both
of them myself!
Uh... Stella...?
(pants)
Oh, that is good!
This is really
good water!
Uh... ah...
You know,
Big Brother...
if it's alright
with you‐
I'd like to train
with you as well!
But... there's already a short
sword master in our family...
Yes but they drove
you away from home.
There is nothing I would
ever want to learn from them!
Alright.
If you think
I can be of help...
Shizuku:
Thank you very much,
Big Brother!
Alright then!
If you're teaching Shizuku‐
then you can teach me too!
Huh? Teach you what?
Is that what's up?
You don't want to?
No, it's not that I don't
want to... I mean I just...
Whatever!
That is just fine!
I don't need you to
teach me anything anyway!
In fact‐ I don't even want you
to teach me anything‐
I just said it to
see what you'd say‐
so you can just forget I
brought it up‐ you hear me?
Nevermind‐ oh great
master Jackass!
Ikki‐ you blockhead...
you insensitive prick...
you pig‐faced
gorilla... you...
Alice:
Well hey there‐
firebrand!
You haven't...
seen Shizuku now have you...?
Oh yeah‐
she's with... huh?
What's... what is that?
I borrowed it
from Kagamin!
"Private School
Prince Academy,"
A.K.A. "Pri‐Pri"!
It's an otome game...
Otome game?
Kazumasa:
I can only see you now.
Stella:
This...might be good...
Kazumasa:
Please. Don't leave me alone.
Stella:
This is how it should be! I want
him to see nothing but me...
Kazumasa:
If I can have you,
then I don't need anything else.
Stella:
Like an unnecessary,
obsessive, delusional, sister?
You won't see
her either‐ will you?
Kazumasa:
So... What do we do now?
Stella:
At least in a game, I can do
what I really want to...
Okay...
Kazumasa:
I... want to be with you, too.
I wish Ikki and I could
do more things like this...
...like holding hands...
And kissing...
And... and... and...
Ikki!
Stella? About
tomorrow, I...
(embarrassed whailing)
What's the matter?
N‐N‐N‐Nothing! What were you
saying about tomorrow?
Yeah um... For tomorrow's
swordsmanship lesson,
I'm gonna take Shizuku and
the other girls to the pool.
So I was wondering
if you wanted to come.
And why would I?!
I mean... it's not like you
really wanna teach me anything
anyway‐ isn't that right?!
About that. I wanted to
explain...
(giggles)
I thought she wasn't
going to come...
She may be
here in body,
but her brain is still
playing "Pri Pri."
Stella, I don't think
I CAN teach you‐
you're already far
too advanced...
Ikki:
Also, our styles
are totally different.
What do you
mean by that?
My style is all
about trickiness...
but yours is all
about strength.
My influence could
only hold you back.
So even if I could
help you at all...
you would only find my
technique limiting and boring.
Stella. I want...
for you to always
go beyond my imagination.
Ikki...
(giggles)
Ikki is mine‐
and I'm his...
That means...
we are lovers...
Soon‐ maybe
we'll...
Students:
(cheering)
(giggles)
(laughs)
Wow, so this
is a Japanese pool.
I guess a princess from the
provinces doesn't know very much
about the
world, huh?
Have you never
seen a pool?
Oh yeah.
But in my castle, we called
a pool this size a bath.
Mmm...
Easy there girls‐
you have an audience.
Mmm...
Girls:
(giggling)
Lessons are
SO paying off!
I can't believe
how awesome this is.
I'm just so
emotional right now...
Mm‐hmm! Mm‐hmm!
THANKS...
you guys...
but it's only been
a couple of days...
Ikki:
(uncomfortable laughter)
Okay now everybody...
I want you to just relax
and let yourselves drift.
Ikki:
We're working to
improve your lung capacity,
but there's another
very important purpose.
"Another purpose"
you say?
It'll become clear
when you do it...
But immersion can be a
catalyst to bring you closer
to your truest self.
While you're in the water,
focus all your consciousness
on the quiet inside of you,
then you'll be able
to hear your own sound.
I know he came here to
continue giving his lessons...
but I wish he would spend
a little time with me too.
I tried really hard
to pick the perfect bikini.
Ooh!
Oh I'm so sorry!
It's okay.
Huh?
Ikki:
Everybody relax,
and listen to your body...
Focus all my consciousness on
the quiet inside of me... huh...
Stella:
Kind of hard to do that when
your brain is so noisy...
Bring me closer
to my truest self...
Help me hear
my own sound...
Yes.
Ikki's Itto
Shura power...
must be a sharpened version
of this sense...
If I can get there,
I can get close to Ikki.
Maybe I can discover something
I haven't seen before.
So...
In my own
consciousness...
Deep inside...
Reaching deeper
and deeper down...
Kagami:
So I'm curious‐ how far have you
and Kurogane gone so far?
Kagami:
So I'm curious‐ how far have you
and Kurogane gone so far?
Mmm!
(coughing)
I'm sorry. I didn't imagine that
question would surprise
you so much.
What do you mean
"how far have we gone?!"
Well you guys
are dating right?
Don't be
ridiculous!
The princess of a nation
dating a commoner like him?
That's insane!
Really...?
Okay then, you wouldn't mind
if I asked him out would you?
Huh?
He's so strong and
handsome...
and he's just
bursting with great stories!...
Alright!... If he's available‐
I'm gonna‐
NO WAY!
Don't you even
think about it‐
he is my boyfriend!
He belongs with me!
(chuckles)
Whoops...
Can I quote you on
that Miss Stella?
Oh...
I'm just kidding‐
I won't tell anyone.
Oh, you won't?
I am a journalist
of integrity after all.
And I want my friends'
romance to blossom and grow!
Thank you, Kagami...
So? How far
have you gone?
Oh!What about
"integrity?"
But I'm so curious‐ I mean you
guys are roommates and all...
I'm talking about your...
sleeping arrangements...?
Do you do the
"master/servant" thing?
OH MY GOD‐
absolutely not!!
Seriously?‐
So he's not all like:
"Nighttime
Itto Shura!"
'cause that's totally how
I've been picturing it...
So you've
only kissed?
We... haven't even
had a... proper kiss.
You hav‐
are you kidding?
Mm‐mmm...
Okay! Now take
a deep breath!
My big brother is
SO dedicated...
he really should just
be teaching me alone...
He does have
a lot to share...
Alice you...
You don't think
it's wrong do you?
That I like
my big brother?
Oh my precious...
the heart wants
what it wants
and I have learned
not to question that.
Alice:
Real love is
never wrong, darling.
Mmm...
I see... this sounds
like the real thing...
Mm‐hmm.
His generosity,
his dedication...
all those things
are so.. dear to me...
But you've been
together for two weeks.
And nothing has
happened like at all?!
Mmm... I don't mean to ask
for too much of him,
but I do wish that we could
behave a little bit more like...
...like lovers.
Have you
told him that?
No, I can't
tell him that‐
A girl is not supposed
to say things like that‐
It's disgraceful!
You know...
I haven't met a guy yet
who doesn't appreciate
a girl taking a
little initiative.
Especially if that girl's
as cute as you are, Shizuku.
Yeah but...
whether or not my brother
could ever accept me...
is a different matter.
Well there's that...
It might require a rather
difficult shift in perspective‐
but it's easier if you've
ever read any Greek drama...
So maybe...
I should just let
him be happy with...
someone else...
Oh sweetie‐
don't make that face.
You still
have a chance.
Listen...
that little princess isn't the
kind who opens up easily...
Guys like him don't easily open
up! YOU have to open up to HIM!
Okay...
But what if he thinks
I'm too forward,
and he doesn't
like me anymore?
He won't "not like" you for
something like that!
Listen‐ guys these
days are like sheep.
They'll mindlessly nibble
the available grass and move on!
Kagami:
What if he runs away because
you weren't quick enough?!
I... couldn't
go on...
Okay!
But seriously...
I guarantee he wants to
take it to the next level!
Kagami:
He was totally lusting after you
when he saw that swimsuit!
Oh my God‐ he was?!
You wait
right here‐
I'm gonna go
get him!
Just tell him you
wanna do it, Okay?
Uhh! Huh? Ahh!
Ikki:
Kagami told me to
come see you.
Did you need
to talk?
Oh... I
uh... wanted...
HEY! What do you
think about my bikini?
Oh... well it... it looks
really good on you...
Wait... he doesn't look
"lustful" to me!
What if he runs away because
you weren't quick enough?!
To tell the truth...
I had something important
I wanted to
talk to you about.
Oh! What's that?
About us...
I mean...
I'm wondering if we
should keep on like this.
Ah...
Huh?
I've been thinking
about it...
It's been two weeks,
and we haven't been acting
like we're together... have we?
So‐ I mean, well,
you know...
Oh... I see.
I'm already
too late...
I've already
lost him...
Because I wasn't
quick enough.
Oh no...
...So I thought maybe we should
talk about whether or not we're
doing the right thing here...
I‐I agree! I was thinking
exactly the same thing!
There is no way this
was ever going to work!
S‐Stella?
Of course, instead of a girl
who doesn't even hold your hand,
you'd prefer someone like
Shizuku, who's all over you,
or Kagami, who's always
rubbing her chest on you!
Wait a minute...
rubbing her... What?
Where the hell is all
this coming from?!
It doesn't
matter!
We're talking about
breaking up, aren't we?!
Wha‐?!
Just calm down...
Don't touch me!
Did I do
something wrong?
Tell me what it was
and I'll apologize, Stella.
Are you mad
at me? Come on.
It's because I know
that you hate me.
How could
I hate you?!
I never said
anything like that!
You don't have to
"say"‐ I know!
No you do not "know" that,
and you can't because
it simply isn't true!
Where did you even
get that idea?
It's pretty clear...
YOU'RE the one who hates me!
No I do not‐ don't be stupid‐
I really like you, Ikki!
Well I like you more!
Oh that's
such a lie!
I SO like
you more!
I know because you wouldn't
even look at my bikini
and I know you
don't care about me
because I wasn't
quick enough!
Stop‐ I'm gonna
get mad!
You're already
MAD, dumbass!
It's because you
are driving me crazy!
This amazing girl
I really like
comes out in a bikini and
she's all cute and hot
and HOW THE HELL DO I NOT
GET EXCITED BY THAT?!
You didn't look interested in my
bikini at all!
Because I didn't want
to objectify you
and make you hate me!
Besides... you say..
you really like me...
but you haven't done anything
to show me that in any way!
I can't just say "I wanna
make love with you!"
I don't want you to think I'm
a... slut... and not like me!
Me, either!
WELL OKAY THEN!
SO WHY THE HELL ARE WE STILL
YELLING AT EACH OTHER?!
I DON'T KNOW ANYMORE!
(panting)
I have an idea.
What?
We could tell each other...
at the same time...
what we want.
Mmm.
I want to... kiss.
Tell me, Ikki...
Would you hate a naughty
girl who would ask her
boyfriend... for a kiss?
There is no guy who doesn't
appreciate a naughty girl.
How 'bout you?
Would you hate a guy
who stares like you're
the hottest thing ever?
Yeah, definitely...
But you're allowed, Ikki.
(phones ringing)
From the student council...?
Renren:
(exerting force)
(giggles)
My next opponent
is Kurogane!
And it's time for me
to show our little princess...
the real power of
the student council!