If you can't achieve, then you
shouldn't achieve.
And that's all I
ever wanted from you.
Utakata:
She's an inspiration and a
comfort to all the kids here...
Ikki:
What could I ever
have hoped for...?
The wielder of an empty...
worthless sword...
Toka:
You guys! You already
made a banner?
Well‐ we don't want to
get too far ahead of
ourselves after all!
It's not even certain
that I'll be in the Seven Star
Sword Art Festival...
Yeah.
When the selection matches
are over, I'll come back for a
little while, sound good?
Alrighty then.
Talk to you soon.
Bye‐bye, Mother.
(phone beeps)
How was the director?
She sound good?
Uh‐huh. She said everyone
is doing really great.
(door knocks)
Uh... coming!
Well hello.
Glad you're here!
Thank you so much
for coming tonight...
Miss Kurogane.
So what happened in your
audience with Madame President?
Oh!
You're aware...
that I'm scheduled to fight
your older brother
in the battle tomorrow...?
Yes.
Those unbelievable
assholes...
I agree.
I don't like the way the
Federation does things either...
But you understand I must
accept their decision.
I've heard that he's not being
kept in very good condition...
Toka:
But I know... that when he walks
out onto that battlefield...
he'll fight with
everything he's got.
And so will I.
Anything less
would dishonor him.
I'll have to fight him with
all my heart and soul.
That's why... I wanted to
ask you for a favor...
She wants you to ask Ikki
to withdraw... God...
So what did you
tell her?
I said I needed
time to.. think...
What do
I do Alice?
Should I ask him to
withdraw from the match?
Only you can answer
that, my love.
You're the only one in your
family that Ikki opens up to.
And you also know first hand,
just how strong Toka Todo is.
If Kurogane... withdraws
from the fight and I win...
or even if he
fights and I win...
Can I be proud... of going
to the national competition
after winning the
battle like that?
I don't know...
It's true.
The match is being fixed
by adults to serve their
own selfish ends...
but you're gonna have to
fight in a way that you
can be proud of‐ Toka...
And I'll bet ya,
that's what Ikki would want.
Yeah. I guess no matter how it
turns out, that's all I can do.
Hangetsu:
Ladies and gentlemen,
it's the final day of the
school's selection match!
We've got a steamy
morning outside,
but the heat
is coming from right here!
Six matches on
six battlefields today,
and those six winners get their
tickets to the Seven Star
Sword Art Festival!
I don't have to tell you...
that all the combatants
today are very tough fighters
who've each won all 19
of their matches so far!
Among them: Princess
Stella Vermillion,
otherwise known as
the Crimson Princess!
Her opponent today is one
of the school's representatives
from last year,
The double‐bladed junior...
Mizuki Ohinata!
But the fight that is getting
everyone's attention today
is this one folks!
One of the top four
fighters of last year's
Seven Star Sword Art Festival,
Toka Todo, vs the unbeaten
F‐rank knight: Ikki Kurogane!
The battlefield is
packed with spectators,
all waiting to see
the battle of the century.
And‐ highly irregular, folks‐
this match is being
broadcast live on TV!
The sound of
the helicopters above us
is only adding to the
excitement down here!
With me is Miss Nene Saikyo...
Miss Ne‐
Oh!
Oh my God, she left me all
by myself up here AGAIN!
Oh my. This is a little
overboard‐ isn't it?
Rather stringent conditions
for the Federation
to allow him to fight
at the school‐ don't you think?
I do. And amidst
all this‐
they've "arranged"
for him to battle Toka Todo.
They're just dying to
watch him fail...
There's only one way for Ikki
to make it out of this intact...
and that is to win this battle.
Oh, I finally found you!
Oh yes...
good morning...
Ugh!
Oh God‐ what are
you doing here?
It was a special
surprise dear!
"Surprise" my ass!
Waddyou want?!
My favorite pupil gives a
colorful greeting as always.
But that's part of what
makes her so adorable!
Adorable?! Well that is
not at all appropriate!
Nene. You know you love
the old man...
Love is gross and old men
are gross and I don't wanna
go near either of 'em!
She's so precious!
(laughter)
Master Torajiro Nango,
welcome to Hagun.
Did you come to see
Toka Todo's fight?
Exactly, she's another
of my favorite pupils.
Though... I probably should've
waited until the Seven Star...
but I just had to see
the Kurogane boy...
Master Nango and Ryoma Kurogane
are relics from
the same bygone era!
Weren't you
lifelong adversaries?
Hmm...
Mr. Akaza...
Sly Akaza...
Unfortunately for everyone,
Master Nango...
It seems increasingly apparent
that today's match
may just have to be canceled.
(snickers)
Canceled?
Female PA:
May I have your
attention, please...
It's already time to start,
but Ikki Kurogane hasn't yet
arrived on the grounds.
According to
selection match rules,
Mr. Kurogane has 15 minutes
to report to the arena
for his battle, or he will
concede the match by default.
Mr. Akaza...
It was the Federation's
responsibility to see that
Mr. Kurogane got here...
And I'm sure there must've
been some miscommunication...
I arrived to collect
the young man myself‐
but he'd already left
on his own...
Akaza:
But... he's a big boy‐
so I'm sure he'll be fine.
(panting)
Unless misfortune befalls
him along the way...
(snickers)
Oh, apparently we'd confiscated
his student handbook...
we thought you'd appreciate
having it back.
(panting)
Ryoma:
Does it frustrate you kid...?
Does it upset you‐
to be the weakest one?
That's good, you hold on
to that feeling. It's proof...
that feeling means
that you are not yet ready...
to give up on yourself.
How much good have those "words
of wisdom" really done for you?
Maybe he was just a crazy,
irresponsible, senile old man...
And you took him seriously‐
and you spent your whole life
trying to live up to an
impossible ideal.
We all have our limits and
our place in this world
is defined by them.
All that
old man did...
was bring you more
pain and loneliness.
And all you got out of it
is this pathetic little sword
that nobody else in
the whole world cares about.
How could such a useless
and ungifted knight
who was tossed away ever
hope to defeat Raikiri?
Don't you think
you've had enough?
Aren't you tired of hanging on
to some old man's nonsense?
Let it go...
You're going
to be alright...
I've got you now...
I don't want
you to go.
Please don't go.
I don't want you
to fight her.
Shizuku...
But I realize...
I would never be able to
stop you even if I wanted...
Back when we were
growing up together...
I can't remember ever seeing
you smile not even once...
But you do when you're here...
and I want you to do
what makes you happy...
Ayase:
Kurogane!
Kagami:
Over here!
Manabe:
Haha! My Main Master!
We're all waiting for you
to get in there
and make us proud
Mister Kurogane!
Kurogane... we all
believe that you can do it!
You had the balls to beat me,
so let's see'em again!
You're the samurai
I respect.
You've gotta keep
striving Ikki. Go get her!
Get in there
and ace her, Master!
Our next front page...
is gonna say "Ikki Kurogane
Wins A Flawless Victory!"
Thanks guys...
You can see that you're
not alone‐ Big Brother.
Look at all
those people.
You've inspired every
single one of them.
And they all
believe in you.
Ikki!
I'm keeping my promise and I am
going to the Seven Star
Sword Art Festival!
Of course.
How could I ever have
questioned it?
Stella... I have
a promise to keep...
It's you and me!
All the way!
A text from Renren...
Kurogane's just arrived.
Well...
Hm?!
I gotta
go... Uta.
Yup! You have a
good battle... Toka.
Hangetsu:
Okay everybody,
the long wait is over!
We'll now begin the
final selection match...
for the Seven Star
Sword Art Festival!
Entering from the East Gate,
it's Toka "Raikiri" Todo,
The Lightning Cutter!
(cheers and applause)
A shining star
on a glorious path,
looking ready for the showdown!
And, entering opposite
her from the West Gate...
it's the Worst One,
Ikki Kurogane!
He's been through Hell‐
and he looks a little
worse for the wear,
But here he is!
Looking lean and mean and
more than ready to do battle!
Miss Alice!
How'd it go?!
(chuckles)
My opponent was
very gracious.
So, how's
our boy doing?
Kurogane is
completely exhausted.
I wonder what
they did to him...
It could be the boy was enjoying
himself and stayed out too late
Akaza:
(snickers)
Toka:
I'm so sorry, Kurogane.
I know that you're
tired and wounded.
But I still can't help...
being excited about
this battle today.
Because ever since...
the first time I saw you fight,
I've been imagining...
What it'd be like to fight you!
I feel exactly
the same way, Toka...
And now that I'm
standing here...
I will not shame you,
or any of the good people
who've shown me support.
I owe you all a great deal
more than that.
Ikki:
So I swear to you...
the only thing that I can.
With all my strength,
I will defeat all of yours!
Hangetsu:
The girl who's remained
at the top,
versus the boy who
climbed up from the bottom.
Their final battle begins now!
Computer:
(buzzer)
Let's go ahead!
ITTO SHURA!
Kurogane has already opened
the match with his Itto Shura!
That's surprising
to say the least!
What's he doing?!
That's so reckless!
Heh.
What, Stella?
So Ikki must've... decided
to do that from the beginning.
He won't use any tricks.
If he wants to beat her...
I'll have to take you head on!
He'll come at me straight ahead.
If I could avoid him once‐
then I'd win...
Not that way!
I'm only gonna get
one good shot.
So... if one's all I get...
I'll give it all my power!
Close‐range is my territory!
The best place for me
to fight is right here!
This... is how I show my respect
to the warrior who faces me...
And this... is how
I'll beat her!
I will will face him...
with my unbeaten Raikiri!
It doesn't matter anymore...
if they set us up!
I'm not fighting to protect
my status in this school!
Ikki & Toka:
I'm fighting... because I want
to beat this knight...
with all the power
I have inside of me!
The Seventh Secret Sword, Raiko!
Raikiri!
I knew from the beginning...
that she's strong...
and I don't have her power.
So I have to gather it all...
and force it out...
I don't need a minute.
All I need is one second!
Sharpen my soul!
Push through...! USE IT ALL!
(panting)
Hangetsu:
GAME OVER!
Todo is down!
One exchange of swords...
one single attack!
One moment later...
Todo and her Raikiri
are shattered into pieces!
Let the winner hear you folks!
(roaring cheers)
The Worst One. No!
Another One! Ikki Kurogane!
Heh.
Wh‐what' the meaning of this?!
Toka Todo must have been
pulling all of her punches!
No, son.
Toka used her power to
its very limit‐
of that I have absolutely
no doubt in my mind! ,/
Nango:
But that amazing boy...
he expanded his limit
at the very last moment.
Huh?! He
did what?!
He wasn't going to beat
Raikiri with Itto Shura.
He put it all...
into one stroke...
Every bit of his power in one
swing, rather than one minute.
(seething)
That one has
far more than power.
More than simple technique...
He has... strength
beyond strength.
And the will of a demon...
Well then we should call it...
the "Itto Rasetsu" from now on.
(giggles)
The boy is so much...
like his grandfather...
I'll never...
allow this... I WILL NOT!
Are you going to do
anything about him?
I think that's about
to get worse...
Whatever he does,
it'll be too late.
Ikki Kurogane just won
all of his arguments
with one stroke
of a sword.
Kurono:
He won't be theirs
to control... not anymore.
Not yet...
I... can't pass out yet...
There's something...
I have to tell her...
Young man... I will
not allow this!!!
You are a failed knight!
You are not worthy of the name
KuroganeYAAAAAAHHHHH...!
Stella:
Outta my way!
You are not worthy of the name
KuroganeYAAAAAAHHHHH...!
Ikki!
Stella...
I'm so proud
of you... Ikki.
Thanks.
But... challenging her
head‐on like that in the
condition you're in...?
How stupid are you?
I know, I know.
Sorry to make you
worry... like that.
It's ok.
I'm stupid too.
'Cause... I've fallen in love...
with a total idiot!
Oh... this warmth...
Ikki:
This warmth... it's
what saved me all along...
I have something
I want to say...
Huh?
What?
Stella.
I want the two of us
to be a family.
Yes! What took you
so long to ask me?!
(thunderous applause)
This is a first!
A marriage proposal
on the field!
AND THE PRINCESS SAID YES!
Itsuki:
This is Kurogane.
Emperor:
Hello, Mr. Kurogane...
It's been a while.
Emperor of Vermillion?
Emperor:
Look what your son has done.
This is obviously big news
in my country as well.
I see. As chief of the
International Federation of
Magical Knights, I apolog‐
Emperor:
There's no need. Kurogane...
let us spare our
children the burden...
of the schemes of adults.
Something I imagine any father
would want for his children.
You agree with me,
don't you... Itsuki?
Kagami:
And then, since the
Emperor of Vermillion clearly
expressed his discomfort,
the whole scandal disappeared
like yesterday's news!
Oh yeah‐ and...
that Akaza guy
was ousted from the
Ethics Committee!
Kagami:
(laughs)
But you probably know
more about that than I do...
So how's your brother?
Is he feeling better?
Uh‐huh! He's... great!
Kurono:
Junior Class, B‐rank,
Kanata Totokubara.
Junior Class, C‐rank,
Kikyo Hagure.
Junior Class, D‐rank,
Botan Hagure.
Freshman Class, D‐rank,
Nagi Arisuin.
Freshman Class, A‐rank,
Stella Vermillion.
Freshman Class, F‐rank,
Ikki Kurogane.
I officially announce these six
representatives of Hagun Academy
for the Seven Star
Sword Art Festival!
(loud cheers)
And now we appoint
our flag‐bearer.
President of the student
council, Toka Todo,
come forward.
Toka:
Yes.
Thank you‐ Director.
I'm very proud to announce
this year's leader...
And it's...
Ikki Kurogane!
Huh?
Uh... but, wh‐why me?!
I think... anybody here could
probably answer that question!
Yeah, Ikki!
"Another One" RULES!
Kurogane, way to go!
(cheers)
Now... please
come here and receive
the school flag, Kurogane.
Ikki:
Oh... Right!
Hey Kurogane...
I am extremely proud...
that I got to battle with you.
Miss Toda...
it was only because...
you were my opponent... that I
was able to exceed myself.
But winning is a promise.
And every victory
brings responsibility.
You carry with you
the hopes and dreams of
all those you've defeated.
So carry ours, with this flag,
to the top of the Seven Star!
Male Student 1:
Ikki's the man!
I promise.
Male Student 1:
Ikki's the man!
Male Student 2:
Hell yeah, Another One!
(cheers)
Stella.
Yep?
Ikki:
You know, I used to think
I didn't care what people
thought of me,
as long as
I knew my own value.
But being acknowledged by others
now... it feels pretty good.
Yeah! 'Specially when it's by
someone... that you like!
Heh.
(birds chirping)
Ikki:
By the way... Stella?
Stella:
What is it, Ikki?
Ikki:
What I said the other day, about
me wanting us to... be a family?
Alice:
Booties incoming!
Shizuku:
Excuse me.
Sh‐Shizuku?
Alice?
You lovebirds only have two more
years until graduation....
In the meantime, I'm going
to teach you everything
you need to know
about being
a Kurogane bride.
First, you must be no closer
to him than one meter
until you're
married.
Stella:
Hey now? What are
you talking about?
Hey! Let's just
take it easy, guys...
Stella:
Hey now? What are
Hey! Let's just
take it easy, guys...
You "take it easy!"
Yup, got it...
I'll calm down...
Shizuku:
No kissing, no conversations
no physical contact of any kind,
these are the Kurogane rules!
Stella:
You just made that up,
like one second ago!
Shizuku:
It doesn't matter when I
made it up. They're rules now.
Stella:
Then kissing 30 times a day!
That's a Vermillion rule!