Ayase:
The Last Samurai...
that was my father,
Kaito Ayatsuji's nickname.
When I was in junior high, he
retired due to a heart problem.
Even when he became unable to
wield a sword like he used to,
he still taught us
and guided us with dignity.
Kaito:
No.
Relax your shoulders
but keep your arms strong.
Tighten your wrists more,
but never strain.
Try to be as natural
as you can be.
Until you've mastered that,
you won't be able to master the
secret technique of Ten‐i‐muho.
Don't strain.
Ayase:
I‐It's hard to do!
Father, maybe it's
impossible for me...
Kaito:
It's not impossible.
Ayase.
You have followed my teachings
with greater devotion
than anyone else
I've ever seen.
Uh...!
Kaito:
I know you've taken it to heart:
"A warrior must never
lose sight of her pride."
"Value civility... Help
the weak. Hate all evil."
The secrets of
Ayatsuji Itto‐ryu...
Ayase:
Are meant to protect people.
That's when I realized...
that my father doesn't...
have very much time left.
That's why he taught
me Ayatsuji Itto‐ryu...
even though I was
still... so immature.
But... Father...
Father...
Stella:
Kuraudo Kurashiki,
a junior at Donro Academy.
What a jerk.
This guy is
really bad news.
He has an ugly habit of
charging in to other schools,
challenging their leaders‐
and then taking their dojos...
Yeah but... he was also one
of the top eight contestants..
at last year's Seven
Star Sword Art Festival...
they call him
"Sword Eater."
Stella:
Sword Eater...
Swordsman killer.
He's a force to
be reckoned with.
Two years ago, when he
challenged my father's school...
Ayase:
...he didn't even
use his device.
He didn't use
any powers?
His sword technique
must be strong...
Ayase:
Yeah...
even my father
couldn't...
That's unbelievable.
Kaito was called the "Last
Samurai..." for a good reason.
I've seen it...
I've seen what he can do.
Ayase:
It was like...
I was living in a nightmare
or something...
Kurado:
(battle cry)
(laughs)
Father!
Father! Please stop!
Sensei! Please‐ that's enough!
I beg you stop this!
Thank you.. both..
for demonstrating such
kindness and concern for me.
I am very proud
of the both of you.
Kaito:
And that is why...
(grunts)
I can never forgive this
animal... for doing harm to you!
The Last Samurai, huh?
Protector of the people?
How noble of you.
That it? That all ya got?
Shit‐ I heard you
were a real badass...
Let's find out... little man.
Father no!
This is my fight!
Stay out of it!
I'll show you, if you wish...
The heart of my sword‐form...
the heart of Ayatsuji Itto‐ryu.
Wha‐?!
Stop!
No...! Father!
I‐...
Father!
I'm...sorr...
I...
Kurado:
I'll give you twenty four hours
to pack up your shit and leave.
You're stinkin' up my new house
with all that blood.
You son of a bitch!
I should've stopped him...
I should've...
stood in front of that bastard
and taken my father's place.
Kuraudo Kurashiki...
has no pride.
He's a reckless barbarian.
And that monster...
took down... my father...
and left him completely
broken and disgraced!
I'm sorry...
Kaito...
Ayase:
This is what's left...
of my father's dojo...
It looks like the
place has rats...
Thug 1:
Check this one out...
Ikki:
Hey you guys...
I'd appreciate it if you could
take me to see Kurashiki...
Thug 1:
What the fuck...?
(doors open)
Well hey! It's the pussy
from the other day.
Kurashiki. I am here
to challenge you.
Yeah?
On behalf... of the
Ayatsuji family,
I'm prepared to fight
you for this school.
(chuckles)
You want my dojo?
Pretty ballsy, kid...
I already kicked
your ass once.
And you know that wasn't the
right time or place for that.
How did she talk
you into it?
It's prohibited for the
knights of Hagun Academy
to use their devices outside
the school without permission.
Unless of course you happen
to be at an accredited
martial arts school
and the master
permits it.
You're not going
to turn me down, are you?
(chuckles)
Interesting!
But before we get into it...
I'm gonna have to make sure
you're even qualified
to take me on.
These guys...
think I am.
Orochimaru.
Easy, boy...
(laughs)
(exerting force)
Come to me, Intetsu.
Ooh nice... that's a
first‐class stance...
Damn I love fucking
up swordsmen!
Alright then...
Are you ready to die?!
(laughs)
Nice reflexes!
(chuckles)
Oops!
My timing
was perfect...
Does he know
what's coming? No...
Bring me his head...
Jakotsujin!
Orochimaru can transform
into anything!
It's impossible to get
out of my reach‐ asshole!
Kurashiki's reach almost
seems to be... endless...
Ikki's not as effective
from range and he has no
way to close the gap...
But it doesn't matter.
Ikki's technique is way more
than this guy can handle.
Poor dumbass...
So that's your next move...
I thought so.
Perfect vision!
Missed me!
His reflexes... I see!
(laughter)
No!
What... did we...
just see?!
(chuckles)
You can dodge that‐
that's pretty good!
I see now.
This ability of yours...
this is how you defeated
the Last Samurai.
The foundation of your technique
is built on a single power...
and that's your
reflex speed.
Ikki:
"To perceive, to understand,
and to respond."
The time it takes to process
and execute all of these things
is called... reflex speed.
It's about three tenths
of a second for most people...
For me and Stella‐ it's about
a tenth of a second,
no matter how much we train.
But I've been watching the speed
of your counterattacks...
And you've actually
managed to get it down to
five hundredths of a second.
Before I can make one move,
you can make two or three...
that gives you quite the
advantage in a battle like this.
With a reflex speed...
that fast...
You can dodge attacks
that would otherwise be
impossible to avoid,
or alter your weapon's
orientation before
it makes contact,
enabling you to strike
spontaneously from a
completely different angle.
This is why his sword
looked like it disappeared
in the middle
of a stroke.
(laughs)
I gotta hand
it to ya‐
you figured out my
"Marginal Counter"
the first time
you fought me.
Big deal...
it won't help you.
There's nothing
you can do about it.
Marginal Counter
is not a technique.
It's a gift
I was born with.
No matter how much
you train your body,
hone your techniques,
Or study your tactics...
Yes. It's meaningless
if it's all overwhelmed
by your natural
reflex speed.
Wow man you are one
insightful little shit...
I hope you don't
die too fast! Hebigami!
Double strikes...
from one attack!
Amateur! You think you can
pull the same trick twice?!
Irregular guarding?
That's right.
It means you're not the only
one who can control distance!
(laughs)
It's not over! Let's see how
you manage this little trick!
A four‐point attack?!
I can't block
them all...!
Huh... Your clumsiness kept
me from killing you that time.
Lucky son of a bitch...
His skill is
truly exceptional!
I'm not gonna give you
a second chance to stumble.
I'll slice you into pieces!
You won't get your school back
if you get involved.
Trust me... I'd like a
piece of him‐ myself...
But look... he's having
so much fun.
He's smiling?
This is his
favorite thing.
Vanquishing
the adversary...
Facing overwhelming strength
and defeating it...
That is all that
Ikki's thinking about.
Hey Ayase...?
Are you sure
the Last Samurai was so
ashamed when he went down...?
What are you talking about?!
Of course he was ashamed!
Ayase:
This... this bastard mocked
my father's honor...
and challenged
him for his dojo...
Cut him down in what should've
been his peaceful years...!
I understand... but it might
not be all that simple...
Stella:
Your father was
a master swordsman, Ayase.
There's a reason people
called him The Last Samurai.
How long do you think such a
warrior could feel fulfilled...
by growing old peacefully?
Stella:
You're right about this guy‐
he is an animal...
But... don't you think some
part of your father...
relished the idea that someone
like this would come along
and challenge him?
And in the end... he went down
just how he wanted to?
His... his final words...
I‐...
Father!
I'm...sorry... I...
I'm sorry... I could
not finish the lesson...
I can see that I was never
a real swordsman...
I never understood...
...the Warrior's Way...
(sobbing)
Father!
Stella:
So that's the
Sword Eater's weakness!
"Marginal Counter" gives him
a whole lot of extra speed...
but no extra
stamina...
Goddamn‐ you are
a stubborn little shit.
Hate to lose...
you know how it is...
Honestly... you've really been
keeping me on my toes,
you're very gifted...
I've been having fun...
I wanted to
make it last...
You're
havin'... fun?
(laughs)
You are my kind
of psychopath!
If you don't mind I...
got a question...
Go ahead...
There's something
I want to know...
about the Last
Samurai...
Ikki:
He was smiling just
like we are‐ wasn't he?
What a stupid
question.
Look, you don't earn a name
like "The Last Samurai..."
If a nice, deadly battle
doesn't make you smile!
Miss Ayatsuji.
With all my strength...
for you and your father...
I'm gonna get
back your two years.
Come! Yamata‐no‐orochi!
Straight ahead?! This kid's
got a death wish!
This is... what the old man
was trying to show me
before he keeled over!
Aw man I waited two whole
years to see this move!
Haaa!
Did... he just use...?
(pained breathing)
Ayase:
My father's final
technique... Ten‐i‐muho!
The soul... of
Ayatsuji Itto‐ryu!
How... How does
he even know that?
Did I... show him...?
Oh yeah‐
"Blade Steal..."
Huh?
(chuckles)
He's done it to me too.
Stella:
Lemme tell ya... that's not all
he steals‐ either....
Alright. What's your name?
Ikki Kurogane.
Kurogane...
We'll finish this at the
Seven Star Sword Art Festival.
What about the dojo.
It was fun while
it lasted...
but I've got bigger
fish to fry, kid.
Uh!
Ikki! Are
you alright?!
Ayase:
Kurogane...
I owe you
an big apology.
All of this is
completely my fault...
I guess I never really
understood anything...
About my father... or what
it means to live as a warrior...
I'm simply not worthy...
to carry on with teaching
Ayatsuji Itto‐ryu.
Ikki:
That's not true.
Huh?
Ikki:
The reason I could win today...
was because you knew
that technique...
you understand Kaito's sword
to the last inch.
Without your understanding
of the style...
I couldn't have used Ten‐i‐muho
in the first place.
No one in the world
is better suited to carry
on your father's legacy.
The true successor of the Last
Samurai should be his daughter.
Maybe she
should...
Thank you...
But if that's the case...
Then I'm gonna... have to train
hard and grow stronger...
Ayase:
My father's successor...
better be a great warrior..
Stella:
So... did you
hear about Ayase?
Apparently she had
a meeting with the
Selection Match Committee...
and admitted to laying all
those traps before your match.
I did.
She was disqualified
from the match,
and got suspended
for 10 days.
She said that she was
gonna take responsibility...
I guess she
really meant it.
(phone rings)
Huh?
Ikki:
Ayase?
What'd she say?
She says that her father's
come out of his coma!
Really?
That's great!
Well... it looks like
that all got wrapped up
rather nicely
didn't it?
Mhmm!
You did
good... Ikki.
Awwww!
Eh?!
Sh‐Shizuku?! Alice?!
C'mon Ikki‐ here‐
let's battle!
Japanese thumb wrestling!
Ready, set, go!
Oh my. I hope we're
not interrupting...
I think we have a
legitimate right to do so...
I mean‐ we were both completely
left out of this whole
"Ayase's Dojo" thing...
Maybe we should go
pick some fights...
Huh?!
Uhh!
C'mon Ikki! I was just
about to beat you!
Well‐ I know I have my own
complications but...
at least I've never been
that high maintenance...
Stella:
Who you callin
"high maintenance"?!
Shizuku:
I'm talkin'
to you‐ Princess.
Stella:
And what exactly about me
says "high maintenance"?!
Shizuku:
It probably takes a team of
people to put your bras on...
Stella:
OH MY GOD!
Shizuku:
They must
be exhausted...
Stella & Shizuku:
(back and forth arguing)