Burn it all! Laevatein!
Ah... ahh! Ahhhhh!
There's the WIN
for Stella!
Hangetsu:
Now at 14 for 14!
(cheers)
(sighs)
(birds chirping)
(stretches)
I feel like I still have plenty
strength left in me today!
I could almost go
fight another match...
(laughs)
Maybe I'm building
up stamina...
Because someone I know
has been torturing me
every day since spring.
Wha...? I was not!
Stella:
I'm just kidding.
You remember...
our promise...?
That we'd both
be selected
for the Seven Star
Sword Art Festival?
And fight each other again
at the finals, right?
We can do it...
We just have to stay undefeated.
Together, right?
(giggles)
(camera beeps)
(snickers)
Kurono:
First of all, congratulations.
Now‐ there's something
I need to ask you...
Do you know a man named Akaza
from the International
Federation of Magical Knights?
Uh!
Ikki:
Yes. I met him a few times
at my parents' house.
He's a member of one of
Kurogane's branch families,
and I believe that he's
working for my father now.
Hmmm... The Federation
put him in charge...
of the Japanese Branch
of the Ethics Committee...
and he's been secretly
sniffing around our school.
I've met your father...
and Itsuki Kurogane is most
certainly a complicated man.
But it's really hard to
imagine that he'd resort
to something so underhanded.
(frustrated sigh)
I think... Akaza is
likely acting on his own.
He's always hated me and
he's never made it a secret.
I see.
Well it sounds like
he just spreads sunshine
everywhere he goes...
Director. If I'm causing
any trouble for the school
I'd willingly‐
Kurogane... it is a grave error
to underestimate me...
And it's my duty as
an educator to protect you.
Ikki:
Thank you
very much, Director.
Do you have
any idea at all...
why the Student
Council wants us?
Nope... I don't
have a clue...
(door knocking)
Ahhh!
Excuse me...
Ouch ouch ouch...
Hey... Uta!
Would you please put the comics
away after you read them?!
Okay...
And Tomaru‐
I keep telling you to put
your weight training equipment
away when you're
done using it!
Yup‐ I'll get
right on that...
We're uh... sorry if we're
interrupting anything.
Oh! A guest!
Hey, are you...?
Ikki:
Toka Todo?
Yes. I haven't properly
introduced myself to you.
Please forgive my rudeness.
I'm Toka Todo, the president
of the student council.
Uh... hi!
It's very nice
to meet you.
Uh, Miss President...?
Yes?
Stella:
Umm... your panties are showing.
Ahhh! Excuse me...
(snickers)
Well, well.
That's our president!
She always
putting on a show...
Are you doing it
on purpose?
No, I am certainly not!
Toka:
Why do you have to be such a
crass little monster?!
Well she... she
Utakata:
Old habits die hard,
Miss President!
from... how
Toka:
I thought you
grew out of all this stuff!
Mmm...
Toka:
I thought you
grew out of all this stuff!
She's much friendlier
Utakata:
Well I'm workin' on it!
She's much friendlier
than I thought she'd be.
Toka:
Oh you little...!
She's much friendlier
than I thought she'd be.
Little Boy:
It's been forever,
Big Sister Toka!
Little Girl:
How have you been?
We missed you!
(laughs)
You guys are
looking well!
Toka and I grew up together
in an orphanage in Fukoaka
that was a lot
like this one.
So... we come and visit
the kids here whenever
we're able to make the time.
We asked you to come
with us because‐
HEY! I've seen that pretty
red lady over there on TV!
Oh! She's the princess
from another country!
Come on! Play with
us please!
(giggles)
Alright then! What would
you guys like to play?
Little Girl 1:
What about kick the can,
big sister?
Perfect!
Little Girl 1:
What about kick the can,
big sister?
I was totally sure the kids
Little Girl 2:
Yeah, yeah! Kick the can!
I was totally sure the kids
would fall absolutely in
Stella:
Alright let's do it!
I was totally sure the kids
would fall absolutely in
Little Girl 1:
Oh my gosh, this is
gonna be awesome!
Little Girl 1:
Oh my gosh, this is
gonna be awesome!
You were right...
(birds chirping)
(children cheering)
Mm‐hm.
Mm‐hm!
Kick the can!
Yeah!
Um, Miss Todo...
we never got much of
a chance to thank you...
What for?
For saving us
back in Okutama.
And for giving my sister...
such a great battle.
Toka:
Oh no, you don't
need to thank me.
Your sister was..
really impressive!
She even forced Toka to
take off her stylish glasses...
I'm certain you've...
figured it out...?
Yes. It was just my
speculation‐ but you can...
increase the accuracy
of your Noble Art...
by blocking your
own vision. Right?
Exactly. I knew
you'd see it.
(chuckles)
Toka:
Human beings...
are like living computers.
Our brain controls our body
by transmitting signals
across synapses,
and these signals are
a weak electrical current.
Since I'm a lightning user,
I can sense that current.
That's my Noble Art:
"Reverse Sight."
All of our thoughts
and actions...
they're all there,
within those transmissions...
And when I block my vision,
I can read an opponent's mind.
That's why...
Ikki:
You were able to anticipate
Shizuku's attacks...
because you could
read her impulses...
Is that how it works?
Yes.
Perfect answer.
I'll take care of
the rest of this stuff.
You guys can go take
a break if you want.
Rawwwr! Get back here!
I'm gonna getchya!
Kurogane?
Is something wrong...?
I don't know how
to explain this, but...
it's like I can't take
my eyes off of Todo...
Utakata:
You're seeing her
real strength...
here with these kids.
This is the core
of who she is..
All her lightning
and her "Reverse Sight,"
They're all insignificant,
if you ask me.
Uh!
Where Toka
and I grew up...
there were a lot
of very troubled kids‐
all with very
complicated stories...
It wasn't...
a very healthy place...
Utakata:
There was this one
in particular...
who was really broken
when he got there.
His own parents
had tried to kill him...
and he was full of hate...
He lashed out at Toka
again and again...
and even though he hurt her...
Toka never gave up on him.
Because of her,
that kid was able to let go
of all that rage and
feel Human again.
Heh. She used to... tell me...
I was very fortunate...
Because before I ended up
in that situation...
my parents gave me
a lot of love.
And though they're gone,
I still have those memories...
and they will always support me.
I want that...
for other people too.
I want to give them memories
that support all of them.
Utakata:
And that's exactly
what she does.
She's an inspiration and a
comfort to all the kids here.
She shows them that no matter
where they come from,
they can become something great
and that they can
be something more.
And that's the true and
real power of Raikiri.
(children chattering)
Om!
(giggles)
Toka:
Alright...
(giggling)
The source of her strength...
is that she uses
her power for others...
and never simply for herself.
That's her power... but do I
really understand the source...
...of mine?
Kagami:
Look! They're back!
Stella! Kurogane!
What's up guys?
Is something wrong?
You two need
to look at this!
What's the...
(gasps)
Ah!
Ikki:
Crimson Princess,
forbidden affair?
Stella:
What?!
Alice:
The press is everywhere.
They love a State Sex Scandal
even more than they love
a celebrity in rehab...
Hmph!
"Her partner Ikki Kurogane‐
well known as Hagun Academy's
worst student...
Under continued investigation
by the Knight Federation
for misconduct..."?!
This is all nothing but lies!
Grrr!
Uh...
Huh?
(snickers)
Who's that?
Mamoru Akaza. One of
our father's henchmen.
Akaza:
Ikki Kurogane.
Based upon recent
developments...
The Federation has decided
to conduct a hearing.
Will you come
with me please?
What? What kind
of hearing?
This is an official summons‐
straight from the
ethics committee...
So you will honor
it of course...?
(snickers)
Are you kidding?!
You can't just run around
pulling people off the street!
Ikki?
It's fine.
I'll be... right back.
This is my problem.
Yeah but...
Alice.
Ikki:
Look after Stella
and Shizuku.
Yep... you got it.
(snickers)
Let's get started, shall we,
young Mister Kurogane?
Precisely when did you
begin your relationship
with Princess Stella Vermillion?
Ikki:
Around the beginning
of the selection match
for the Seven Star.
It was after my
first match ended.
And did it not occur to you
that an indecent relationship
with a foreign princess,
might not be an advisable
course of action?!
Pardon me, Sir, but the princess
and I have engaged
in no indecent beha‐
Akaza:
Ikki, Ikki...
You will be informed when
we are prepared to allow you
to make your statement.
Akaza:
Impertinence has no
place here, son.
Forgive me, Sir.
However, I must insist
on making this very clear.
Now, Ikki...!
I love the Princess
and she loves me.
Our intentions are as
pure as they are serious.
We've done nothing wrong...
And I cannot simply
stand here and stay mute,
while you try and tell us
that we have!
What they're really after
is a full confession:
"I did it... I defiled
the princess and dishonored
my family's good name..."
That's what they're trying to
get from Kurogane‐ isn't it?
Mm‐hmm...
but the national branches
can't simply disqualify a knight
of their own volition...
Right... but
that slimeball Akaza
will stop at absolutely
nothing to get what he wants...
Kurono:
Oh, I know...
The hearing resumes
at six in the morning sharp.
Go to sleep now.
Game over! Stella is
on fire! 15 for 15!
Male Student 1:
Did you see the news?
Male Student 2:
I know! Those two are
in so much trouble!
I heard they are
sharing a room!
Male Student 3:
I bet it gets real
steamy in there man!
Male Student 4:
Heh, she prob'ly
burns the bed!
Hmph. That's a
They have no idea
what they're up against!
She's got nothin'
in her way!
Oh, doesn't she...?
Ikki...
Selection match here?
Instead of the academy...?
Yes! We would certainly
never wish to interfere
with your other duties.
Chief Akaza did you
a favor! Be grateful!
(snickers)
Ikki:
Ah! Miss Yuri!
Kurogane...
No private
conversations!
Get in your starting
position prisoner!
(snickers)
Akaza:
Let's go ahead!
Kagami:
"Ikki Kurogane narrowly
wins the battle...
his face showing no
expression of remorse."
It's just more
Ethics Committee propaganda.
Alice:
They're dragging Ikki through
all the mud they can muster.
Isn't that the girl?
Alice:
They're dragging Ikki through
all the mud they can muster.
It is!
Could all this
be my fault?
Maybe I... should
just let him go...
STELLA!
Stella!
Shizuku‐ what's
your problem?!
That's my question.
What is YOUR problem?
Is it possible
that you don't understand
why my brother is putting
himself through all of this?
Shizuku:
It's because he couldn't deal
with the fact
that his relationship
with you was violated
by their obscene intervention!
That is why!
That's what you mean to him!
That's how much
my brother loves you!
Stella...
I want to stand
in front of everyone...
and tell them how
I feel about you...
Shizuku:
If you don't
even understand that,
if you dare walk
away from him...
I will never forgive you.
Me neither...
Stella:
Ikki is doing
this to protect me.
He is fighting them for me.
But what... can I do...?
What can I do?!
(snickers)
That's it!
Ikki Kurogane wins!
Well done, son!
(panting)
Easy Kurogane, it's okay...
Do not touch
him ma'am!
Yeah, yeah...
Mm... bleeeeeegh!
What the hell?!
Alright... I'll see you
at your 17th match.
What's the matter
with her?
(snickers)
A messy but
impressive trick.
(panting)
(gasps)
Ikki:
Stella's fighting...
and she's winning...
She is going to
keep our promise.
And so will I.
No matter what happens...
Or... who tries
to get between us...
Let me speak
with my father.
Pardon?
My father... Itsuki Kurogane
is the branch leader.
I'll take my appeal
directly to him.
(snickers)
Patently ridiculous!
Is this why you asked to see me?
Huh? What?! Impossible!
Why would he interrupt
in the midst of...
Oh!
Could this be the
little vixen's doing...?
Kurogane. I'm afraid...
it's time to face your past...
Father.
I heard... you're
winning all your matches.
and that not all of your
opponents are weak
or low‐ranking.
That's quite... something.
(heart pounding)
Father...
Ikki:
I thought I was done...
done with you,
done with this family...
I didn't want to be what
you were making me in to.
It's what fueled me and
kept me going into battles....
But now I see you here
in front of me...
and all I want...
all I ever wanted...
Father‐ I...
I'm working very hard.
My rank is still F,
but I'm getting...
getting much stronger
every day...
If I could make it to
the Seven Star... if I won...
would you...
acknowledge me then?
I see.
You thought all this time
that you weren't acknowledged
because you were simply weak.
If that is so‐ you've made
a terrible error.
I have always acknowledged you.
However... teaching our family
techniques to someone without
significant talent...
is a futile exercise for both
the teacher and the student.
Huh?
But, futility is not
the worst thing.
It's far worse to
imagine mediocrity
as something toward which
we should strive.
Much as you're doing now.
Itsuki:
When mediocrity rises‐
it demeans us all.
When we celebrate
the untalented,
more untalented seek
to follow their example.
And that's something this
organization can't allow.
Ikki:
I see. It wasn't that
my father hated me...
Itsuki:
Ikki:
It was that he never...
had any expectations of me...
Itsuki:
Ikki:
It was that he never...
had any expectations of me...
Itsuki:
Your place in the pecking order
is decided the very
moment you're born...
Ikki:
and you can't fail a man who
expects nothing from you...
Itsuki:
If you can't achieve,
then you shouldn't achieve.
And that's all
I ever wanted from you.
What are you crying about?
I'm nothing to him. And I've
always been nothing to him...
(snickers)
Poor little... Kurogane...
Ikki:
Until today...
all I wanted from my father...
was for him to tell me
that I was worthy...
But I will never
be worthy of him...
Not to him...
and not to anyone else...
Ever...
I had no idea
it went so deep.
Yes... I know...
I never imagined that he could
still have such feeling for our
father.
Timing couldn't be worse...
but I have news...
It's time that you learned
who you're facing next.
It's Toka... "Raikiri" Todo.
Inquisitor 1:
Your opponent for your
final‐round selection match
has been decided.
The Ethics Committee
has grown tired...
of this embarrassing debacle...
Inquisitor 2:
If you wish to prove your
qualifications as a knight,
then win this duel and see
these questions put to rest.
Duel...
(snickers)
If you win the match
against Raikiri...
we will no longer persue
this inquiry against you.
But if you lose today...
you'll have to give up these
ambitions of becoming a Magical
Knight for good.
I understand.
(snickers)
Akaza:
The match will begin
at 11 am tomorrow.
Stella:
Ikki...