Mikazuki:
There it is! It's "Mach Grid!"
By accumulating her
own speed, she accelerates
exponentially until she stops!
That's the Noble Art
of Renren Tomaru,
also known as
"The Runner's High,"
and she's already broken
the sound barrier folks!
Aren't you surprised,
Kurogane?
Yeah. You've earned your place
on the student council, Tomaru.
You're too fast
for my eyes to follow.
Hangetsu:
Look out folks!
Saijo is swinging his Zanbato!
My ability is "the accumulation
of slashing momentum"!
The more I swing it‐
the heavier it gets!
You've already lost
your chance, Vermillion!
This is... the Noble Art of
"the Destroyer‐" Ikazuchi Saijo!
Hangetsu:
Is this the end
for Stella Vermillion?!
Crescendo Ax!
Black Bird!
Oh!
Huh?!
Don't forget‐
"Mr. Secretary"...
My Knight ranking
is an "A".
I can bring down any special
ability, any power, any trick...
and I can do it head‐on.
You... you've beaten me...
Mikazuki:
Another win! for Ikki Kurogane,
A. K. A. "Another One"!
Victory over a
student council executive!
He remains undefeated!
This year's freshmen...
continue to astound!
Mikazuki Tsukuyomi signing off!
And This is
Hangetsu Tsukuyomi...
We'll see ya next match!
(cheers and applause)
Mmm...
Shizuku:
Congratulations,
Big Brother!
Heh. I think I hurt my
wrist on that one...
Are you alright brother?
Would you like me to sleep
by your side and nurse you?
Huh?
He can't heal
if he's suffocating!
Ikki, you've gotta
break free from her! ,/
But, Big Brother...
You wouldn't neglect
your little sister
who loves her brother with
her whole heart‐ would you?
Oh... No...
of course not...
Ya hear that‐
Princess?
You have nothing
to do with us,
so stop butting
in our conversation!
I have something
to do with him!
Really? And what's that‐
I wonder?
IT'S...
nothing...
Oh...
Alice:
Ikki, Honey?
Just curious‐ how long are
we going to let this go on?
Oh... I guess you
spotted her too, huh?
But Big Brother...
what are you talking about?
Ikki:
Well... uh... I think
I'm being followed by someone.
What?!
A stalker?!
Oh my God!
Wait... so a
"stalker" is what?
Like someone who sends you
a shaving kit in the mail?
No Stella.
It's a razor blade.
Who would send you
an entire shaving kit?
Oh shut up
I don't know!
A shaving kit includes
a razor blade!
She has been shadowing
you for a week...
Alice:
And not well‐ I thought it was
some sort of performance piece.
Perhaps we should
make contact?
You're right.
I guess it's time we...
find out who she is...
Alice:
Okay I see you
back there.
Is there something
you need?
Uh... ahhh!
Uh...
Shizuku:
Who is this...?
Stella:
Well, I've seen
her somewhere...
Uh, hold on a minute,
this is just a misunderstanding!
I... I uh...
Ikki:
Oh wait you're...
Uh... Umm... Wahh!
Oh...
Ayase:
Uh... Thank you
for pulling me out...
I um... Let me see.. I uh..
I'm a junior.. and uh...
Is something wrong?
No, I just...
I'm embarrassed to look
into a boy's eyes...
I'm sorry...
Well isn't she
just precious?
My name's...
Ayase Ayatsuji...
in Class... 3‐1.
Ayatsuji...
Ikki:
Are you by
any chance...
related to
Kaito Ayatsuji?
Oh... well yes I am,
Kaito Ayatsuji is my father.
No wonder!
Ikki:
When I saw that callous from
practicing the bamboo sword
I thought you must be!
Hey, Alice.
Who's Kaito Ayatsuji?
Wow, this is amazing. Kaito's
sword technique is flawless!
I'm... afraid
I haven't met him...
Wow, this is amazing. Kaito's
sword technique is flawless!
I'm... afraid
I haven't met him...
He was a gifted
swordsman...
called "The
Last Samurai..."
The Tenryu Gozen Match,
The Tozai Toitsu Match,
The Musashi Cup,
The Judan Match...
He won all the well‐known
tournaments,
and enjoyed his glory in
the world of the Japanese sword.
He's a true master.
But he's not
widely known...
because he happens
to not be a blazer.
Ikki:
When I was little,
I used to study swordplay
by watching the
videos of his matches.
Seriously?!
Of course! I can't believe
I'm meeting his daughter...
It's so cool!
I haven't heard his name
very much lately though.
How is he?
Uh...
There was an accident
during a match...
and he's in the
hospital right now.
Ikki:
O‐Oh, I'm sorry.
I'm so sorry‐
I had no idea...
No‐ no‐ please‐
it's okay!
I'm happy to know that a
swordsman like you...
is also a big fan
of my father...
means a lot.
So thank you!
But more importantly, I think
it's time you tell us all
why you've been
stalking my brother.
I'm pretty sure I recognize
that hungry look you have
in your eyes when you're
staring at him.
So what would be the
best way to punish you?
That hungry WHAT?!
So what would be the
best way to punish you?
N‐No! It's not like
that I promise!
Iron maiden,
barbed whip...
Shizuku:
nail ripping, burning with fire,
waterboarding, ant hill,
bondage...
walk of shame, wooden horse
torture, public stockade...
I've been... practicing
Ayatsuji Itto‐ryu...
tying you up and letting
vultures eat your eyeballs...
and I've just
suddenly hit a wall...
But I...I just
couldn't figure out...
how to approach a man
I didn't even know...
I'm sorry...
All this time, you've been
trying to figure out how
to talk to me?
Yeah...
I'm so embarrassed...
Mystery solved.
(sighs)
I'm really sorry!
Miss Ayase...
I would be honored
if you would join me
for training.
(gasps)
Students:
(battle cry)
(wooden swords clash)
Ikki:
No wonder she has
a solid foundation.
She never forgets the forms,
but isn't fixated on them.
Very high level.
However...
Ayatsuji. Stop a moment.
Mmm?
what do you need,
Mister Kurogane?
I was thinking...
the reason you
feel like you're stuck...
is because you worry that you're
not reaching Kaito's level?
Yes, exactly!
No matter what I do...
I can't move
as fast as my father...
Even though I have all
of his moves down perfectly!
Ikki:
That's the problem.
(gasps)
Imitating Kaito
like that...
is the only thing
getting in your way.
Are you saying my
father is wrong?!
Not at all.
Ikki:
You and Kaito are
different genders...
Which means that your
anatomy and your muscle
development are also different.
Your father's technique
is so perfect,
the differences
are apparent...
Right...
I do understand... ,/
No wonder you're
so amazing, Kurogane!
I think I might
have an idea...
about how I can help you...
If you want to correct it...
Mm‐hmm!
However...
Huh?
Ikki:
If you feel strongly about using
exactly the same sword technique
as your father,
then you shouldn't
force yourself to change that.
Because once you correct this...
there'll be no going back.
I want to learn...
I want you to help me become
a better swordsman please.
Alright.
You can trust me.
Raise your sword.
O‐Okay...
Huh?!
(gasps)
Wh‐Wh‐What are you doing‐
Ikki‐ OH MY GOD!
In order to
correct her form...
we have to
fix her stance...
Ikki:
Ayatsuji... I know
you're embarrassed...
just hang
on a sec...
Wha... okay then...
I'm gonna move you
a few millimeters.
There we go.
Now do you feel
the difference?
Focus on that
and lock it in.
Oh yeah I
feel... that...
Females have a huge
advantage over males...
when it comes to
flexibility.
Especially here...
The female pelvis is
shallower for pregnancy,
which changes your
center of gravity.
And... it gives you a much wider
range of motion than a male,
and better
lateral movement.
It's an advantage
only females have.
If you move your entire
body using the hip joint,
then all your moves will
become one step faster.
(slight moaning)
(horrified gasp)
Okay... that
should it.
I'm sorry if that was
uncomfortable... you alright?
Yes I'm fine...
(uncomfortable laughter)
Alright.
Raise your sword.
Okay...
Ikki:
And...?
It feels
a little... tight.
You'll get
used to it.
Just feel the
difference. Here!
(gasps)
Yeah, that's
totally better.
Mmm!
Oh I see...
Alice:
So when she defends herself,
she absorbs the impact
into her lower body‐
instead of
her arms.
Wow! You're
so great, Kurogane!
This was troubling me
for a long time,
and you just fixed it
so easily!
You're a professor
of swordsmanship!
That's great.
I'm not so sure I'm thrilled
about the title, though...
(laughs)
Mmm...
Ikki:
I'm sorry
about earlier...
I mean if I...
made you uncomfortable...
Not at all‐ I'm deeply grateful
for your help‐ Kurogane.
And you... you have very...
big and rugged hands...
They're like... my father's
hands‐ and that made me happy.
I guess I never
saw them that way...
Oh but I
like them...
I think they're
really nice!
They're the hands of
an incredibly lovely man.
Oh...
Oh, I'm sorry‐
I didn't mean to say‐
I mean I wasn't trying to‐
It's not that I want to‐
I mean I was jus‐
No‐ I understand‐
it's okay!
Shizuku, you
must be dying.
I mean you saw the way
that he was touching her right?
How silly.
He's just giving a
lecture on swordsmanship.
And unlike the
Pig Princess,
she's not trying
to trick my brother
into getting into
bed with her...
Who you callin'
a pig?!
Besides...as long as it makes
my big brother really happy...
I'll be okay if I'm
not the one with him...
Huh?
If my big brother finds someone
who makes him truly happy‐
even if it isn't me...
as long as they never betray him
or bring him sorrow,
then I will be happy for him.
It's just... I don't think
there's anyone other than me
who can do that...
not like I can.
Shizuku... that was extremely
mature... for a kid...
And maybe you have
a child's brain
because all you developed
were your breasts.
Or maybe your
huge thighs...
My huge what?!
I feel... like I
could get stronger...
if we could just... continue
our training... together.
So would it be alright with you
if we could do this again?
Of course!
I must...
I must make
myself stronger.
Ayase:
I have to win
the selection matches...
and make it to the
Seven Star...
Hey, Ikki?
Yeah?
Stella:
How was it? Touching
Ayatsuji's body everywhere?
I‐I have nothing
to say about that.
Ikki... here...
Stella,
I was only trying to help her
improve her stance‐ I promise.
I know, but...
I just... I just felt a
little insecure that's all...
Don't you worry.
The one that I need...
is you, Stella.
Ikki...
You are getting much faster!
Thank you... Miss Stella!
Ayase:
Thank you so much for
helping me, Kurogane!
This is totally
my treat today...
so you two go ahead and
order whatever you want!
Thank you,
Ayatsuji...
but uh... Stella...
are you still hungry?
I can't help it.
I need to eat this much
or my body doesn't
move well.
I see.
But four servings of
mixed grill,
and three large
steaks...
Ayase:
and you can still keep
that slender waistline?
I don't get it.
Yeah.
(nervous laughter)
Since I started
practicing with you,
every day... has been a
major discovery for me.
Little by little...
slowly but surely...
I feel so much closer
to my father every day.
Mister Kurogane...
I can't thank you enough.
Don't thank me‐ it's all
because of your hard work.
And besides‐ I'm certain
that eventually...
you'd have figured
it out yourself.
Eventually wasn't
gonna cut it...
to get back what was
taken from me.
Yo, it's you, Ayase!
(gasps)
Hey, it's Ayase!
We haven't seen
you in forever!
HEY GIRL!
Wassup?
(chuckles)
Thug 1:
Hey, bitch! Don't ignore Kuraudo
when he's talking to you!
Excuse me, but you're
being rude.
Could you leave us?
What?! Who the
fuck are you?
Thug 2:
Someone wants to
get his ass kicked!
You're a swordsman,
aren't you?
Heh.
Hey that's my bad‐ bro.
Sorry to interrupt.
I just saw an old face,
so I had to say hi.
Let me offer an...
apology.
Sure, with
pleasure...
(chuckles)
A swordsman should
really keep his guard up
Ikki!
Kurogane!
Kuraudo,
you're so bad!
(customers panicking)
Thug 1: YOU ARE ON THE
FUCKING EDGE DUDE!
(growls)
(gasps)
(giggles)
Kurado:
Listen up, asshole.
There's nothing
I like better
than destroying weak little
sword‐swingers like you.
So, Let's get it on...
You have your device, don't ya?
You pieces of shit!
I'm gonna send you back
to your families in an ashtray!
Stella.
His hand...
must've just slipped.
It's nothing to fight about.
Wh‐What the
hell are you...?
Thug 1:
(laughs)
Seriously? This guy got his head
busted and he's still smiling.
This sorry bastard
doesn't have any balls on him!
Hey it's natural to be
scared of Kuraudo,
but where's your
fucking pride man?!
Female Thug:
(giggles)
Look at him!
Fuck it.
Messing with a baby like him
isn't good for the reputation.
Let's go dudes.
Bye‐bye, baby boy!
You're lucky man‐ Kuraudo
doesn't bother with weaklings.
Thug 2:
You can change your
diaper now baby!
What are you
doing, Ikki?!
Letting these jackasses
say all they want!
Ikki:
I mean, you obviously took the
first blow on purpose!
(gasps)
If I avoid it, it could
complicate things.
I can't use my device
in a place like this.
I could get expelled.
Th‐That's true, but...
You really didn't
need to use Intetsu
to get rid of those jerks.
I'm not so sure...
Hm?
He's very strong.
Ayase:
(whimpers)
Oh Wow, what a disaster,
what a misfortune.
Huh?
You've just met Kuraudo
Kurashiki‐ the Sword Eater.
He's the ace
of Donro Academy...
and he just picks on any and
everyone who gets his attention.
But... you made a very
good call, Mr. Kurogane.
Because he was one of the best
eight in last year's
Seven Star Sword Art Festival.
Kanata:
(giggles)
Yes, that's absolutely right.
If you actually did
resort to violence...
then I'd have had no choice
but to take every single one
of you down right here.
Ikki. Who are they?
Ikki:
The Vice‐President of Hagun
Academy's student council,
Utakata Misogi... and the
treasurer, Kanata Totokubara.
Student council...?
Yeah... lemme see
what I can do about your wound.
At least I can...
make it feel better.
Hey Kurogane...
Are you gonna
be alright?
Yeah... thanks to Misogi...
It almost feels...
like the wound itself
has completely disappeared.
But more importantly...
who the hell are they?
If you don't wanna answer that‐
you don't have to.
Ikki:
But... if you're in some
kind of trouble with them,
then I hope you'll
let me help you.
Kurogane, I...
Thug 1:
That was awesome, what a coward!
Thug 2:
Oh man did you guys see
the look on his face?!
And how can he just keep smiling
after that? What an idiot!
Thug 3:
Maybe he's just smart enough to
not go against Kuraudo.
Female student:
One, two, three...
Students:
She was so dedicated‐ where the
hell is she? It's weird.
Well I'm sure the princess
is enjoying the sudden
decline in competition...
You were so obviously
jealous of her.
That's not even what I was
talking about!
Oh I'm sure you weren't...
"giant hippo legs."
You better
shut up!
Shizuku:
Well they're huge.
Stella:
They're normal,
half‐pint!
Shizuku:
That's what you
think, ya cow.
(bird chirping)
Alice:
So you... haven't
heard anything from her?
Um why?
If her goal is to make it to the
Seven Star Sword Art Festival,
then she can't lose even one
fight in the selection match.
But she has no chance of winning
tomorrow in the match with you.
Alice:
And if that's
the case...
Then our girl has to make
her move on you before then.
Am I right?
You don't miss much‐
do you Alice?
And she sets her trap...
Not Ayase. She would never
do something like that.
She put all her
faith into my hands... ,/
so I'm going.
It'll be fine.
Oh you are
so... shiny...
I'm "shiny"?
Yeah, shiny.
You're sorta
like the sun.
I do envy you, that.
I usually can't bring myself
to look at people straight on.
However, I've grown quite adept
at seeing from the angles.
You know‐ honey, you might have
to be prepared to end your
friendship with her.
You can't let her get into
your head and shake you...
Thank you... ,/
But I won't be shaken‐
no matter what.
Ikki:
I'm going to keep the
promise I made to Stella.