Tsukuyomi:
It has finally begun...
The selection match for the
Seven Star Sword Art Festival.
Vermillion's first
opponent is Momotani,
also known as:
"The Heavy Tank"!
His "Goliath" is a
very rare armor device,
and with it, he releases
a Heavy Charge.
Will we get to see it
explode today?!
(students cheering)
Male Student 1:C'mon, Momotani!
Male Student 2:
No one can beat you in
close‐range combat!
Male Student 2:
No one can beat you in
close‐range combat!
Male Student 3:
She lost to an F‐rank!
Male Student 4:
Show her the power
of a senior student!
Male Student 4:
Show her the power
of a senior student!
Stella:
Unlike all your screaming fans
up there in the stands,
you seem to get the picture.
This is a
real fight...
These aren't
phantom forms,
so you know if
you jump right in‐
you are gonna
get burned alive.
Stella:
Think good and hard before
you make your next move.
(panicked breathing)
(armor rattles)
Ha... I... give up!
Female P. A.:
Winner: Stella Vermillion!
(students cheer)
(giggles)
Alice:
An A‐ranked knight really
is so much stronger.
Shizuku:
It's nothing to be
too proud of.
Her opponent was
disappointingly inadequate.
Oh, now‐ honey‐
come on...
Stella:
No, as far as
today's concerned‐
Shizuku
is right.
I heard you both
won your bouts...
Alice:
Yes! Triumph
all around!
You were all totally awesome!
Stella:
(screams) Kagami!
Don't scare me like that!
(excited giggle)
I'm sorry.
But I saw three first year
winners all together
and I got excited!
Uh...
Who are
you‐ sweetie?
Kagami:
Oh, excuse me!
My name is
Kagami Kusakabe!
I'm a member of the
school's newspaper club!
Ooooh! A
journalist!
I'll bet you just get all
the interesting news don't you?
Hmm... Well‐ I am
a serious journalist...
I mean I'm not writing a
gossip column or anything.
But I do hear
all kinds of things...
Well hello‐
my newest friend.
Can I call you
"Kagamin"?
Sure!
Alice & Kagami:
(evil snickers)
(video tracking)
(pained cries)
(gasps)
(sighs)
(door opens)
Stella:
I'm back, Ikki.
Stella...
Congrats!
I saw the results.
Hey‐ it's me‐ you know.
What did you expect?
Heh, of course.
Stella:
Have you been watching
this all day?
Ikki:
Yeah. I want to see
what his timing's like.
That's
"Area Invisible"?
That's his...
technique‐ huh?
Stella:
So he can hide everything‐
sight, scent,
air pressure changes...
total imperceptibility?
Yeah. A feature of
his device, Oborozuki.
Ikki:
It's a
tricky one.
Stella:
Attacking his enemy
from complete concealment.
How slimy. I don't like
the way he fights.
(chuckles) Yeah, but if
you were his opponent,
he'd withdraw
from the battle.
What?
Ikki:
With your array
of wide‐ranging attacks,
you could easily overturn
his Area Invisible.
He'll uh... always try to
avoid an opponent like that.
Seriously...?
Ikki:
His un‐knightly approach
has earned him a nickname:
"The Hunter."
Stella:
Where I come from‐
they call that "a coward."
But... he's gonna be
a tough one for you.
Hmm.
He's the worst possible
match‐up for me...
Are you gonna
be... Okay?
Are you worried
about me, Stella?
What? I'm...
not at all!
I just don't want you to
lose to a guy like that!
I see.
I... what
do you...?
Don't worry. I think
I've got a way.
I will...
defeat him.
Oh... you will,
I know!
Stella:
You've got this.
Ikki:
Yeah.
(panting)
I canNOT lose to him...
Well‐ hello...
stranger...
Alice...
Can we talk?
You got a sec?
Sure. What's up?
Alice:
I heard a rumor that
there was some bloodshed
between you and
Shizuya Kirihara last year.
That true?
(sighs)
Ikki:
Last year, my family
had connections
with the previous
director of the school,
and they were trying
to get me kicked out.
So Kirihara thought
I was a good target.
Kirihara:
Hey, is it true that
you can't attend classes
because your
scores are too low?
Yeah it's true.
Hey... I know....
You want your teachers to
recognize your ability?
Why don't you show 'em
how you stand up in a duel
with a real talent?
Right here
and right now.
No thanks. I'm not
dueling with you.
(chuckles)
C'mon now man!
I'm only trying to
help out a fellow student!
(arrow fires)
AHH!
That looked like it really hurt!
(teasing laugh)
Why don't you fight back?!
Ngh.
Oh, you better
make your move, dude,
because no one in this
school is gonna give a shit
about helping out
The Worst One!
Ikki:
I knew if I summoned my device,
I'd have gotten expelled...
even if I only used it to try
and avoid the fight...
So you couldn't
even defend yourself?
Ikki:
Mm‐mm.
It's the only reason
I'm still here.
Alice:
Ikki... if things
hadn't changed...
if you were still being
barred from classes
and official events...
what would
you have done?
Ikki:
I'd still be here.
I will demonstrate
my strength. I will...
No matter how many years
it takes me.
Alice:
I get you.
I really do.
Ikki...?
I think you've been hurt
you so many times...
you're used to it.
Alice:
Strength is nothing but
tolerance, sweetie.
Just resistance
to accumulated stress.
Our brain has funny ways
of showing us
when we're about to
reach our limit.
Anger, sadness,
irritation...
They're all just
smoke signals.
But honey, you...
You've already tolerated
so very much...
You can't even
read the signs anymore...
That's why...
Your face is always such
a mask of perfect serenity.
Sorry Alice,
I don't get it...
Yeah...
Alice:
Ikki‐ my greatest
hope for you...
is that someone's gonna come
along who can read those signs.
As your friend...
I think you've earned that.
Stella:
You still have a little time
until your standby hour.
Do you wanna...
maybe watch some
of the other battles?
No thanks. I think I'm
going to the waiting room.
I want to concentrate
on my fight.
Oh uh...
Big Brother?
Your shoelace...
Oh, thank you,
Shizuku!
Be careful out there.
Computer:
This selection match is
full contact and may cause
injury or death.
If you understand this
and wish to continue,
please press "Agree."
Nene:
(giggles) Wow, you didn't even
have to think about it, did you?
Up through junior high school‐
all matches are conducted in
phantom form;
so many students seriously
hesitate at this point.
I've been waiting to fight
an official match...
I won't hesitate.
Oooh, very cool‐
I'm impressed!
You're Nene Saikyo,
aren't you?
Nene:
Oh yeah? So you know
my name‐ do you?
Ikki:
The Demon Princess
of the KOK Top League?
There's no one in this school
who doesn't know you.
Well, I suppose.
I also heard that you and
the Director are old friends,
and that you'll be working as a
part‐time instructor this year.
Yes, yes, that is correct.
So, what do you say?
How about...
if maybe tonight I give you
a very special private lesson?
Uh... I don't...
Kurono:
Dammit. Would you get away
from my student please?
Ahh! You startled me!
Don't do that, Ku‐chan. I could
very easily have killed you.
Not even on your
best day‐ sweetheart.
Moving on... our third
match seems to have
lost its supervisor.
(nervous laughter)
Well‐ it was a terribly
boring fight‐
so I just decided...
(whack)
Kurono:
Get back to your post,
you walking public indecency!
Okay, okay, I'll go ‐
stop pulling my hair!
Thirty more minutes left...
gotta concentrate...
Ikki:
I finally made it here...
...to my first official match.
I fought for it...
...and now I get my chance.
I cannot... will not lose.
(gasp)
Wh‐what is...this?
Distorted PA:
Ikki Kurogane to
the battlefield please.
Ikki Kurogane to the
battlefield.
(sighs)
Here we go...
(cheers and applause)
Hangetsu:
Look at this!
The biggest field in the school,
the Great Arena,
is utterly packed
with eager spectators!
This is Hangetsu Tsukuyomi...
on play‐by‐play,
and here with me...
instructor and commentator
Nene Saikyo!
Great to
be here...
Hangetsu:
You'll be glad you
didn't miss this match!
Our first combatant,
already a veteran of the Seven
Star Sword Art Festival...
C‐rank knight, Shizuya Kirihara!
Female Student 1:
Shizuya!
Female Student 2:
He's so cool!
Our other contestant,
an F‐rank knight who recently
defeated Stella Vermillion
in a mock battle...
Ikki Kurogane!
Kirihara:
I can't believe
you actually showed up.
I guess I get to
beat you up like a
rag doll, right Worst One?
You can try... Shizuya.
(chuckles) It's time to
go hunting. Oborozuki!
Heh, heh.
Come to me, Intetsu.
(buzzer)
Computer:
Let's go ahead!
Whoa, that's such
a hard stare!
I don't think I like the way
you're lookin' at me, Kurogane.
The battle has already
started... Kirihara.
(chuckles) Jeez man‐
you are so uptight!
But if you're in such a hurry...
(synthesizers play)
Hangetsu:
There it is!
Area Invisible!
Kirihara has
disappeared from view!
It really is a
tricky ability, but...
there's a way
to beat this!
Hangetsu:
And Kurogane
deftly deflects!
There you are!
Ugh.
Did we... Did we just
get a glimpse? Amazing!
Hangetsu:
Did Kurogane somehow
find Kirihara?
Nene:
That's right. Kirihara's
Area Invisible...
doesn't extend to
his arrows.
Kurogane calculated
his location...
by tracing their
point of origin..
Well my goodness.
Is it possible you actually
intend to win this battle?
I wouldn't be here...
if I didn't.
Kirihara:
(laughs) You haven't even
changed a little bit, have you?
It's cute... but
it's really annoying.
Just keep shooting.
Let your arrows fly.
I'll knock 'em all
away, "Hunter."
Hmph. The Worst One's got a
mouth on him‐ doesn't he?
Kirihara:
Tell ya what: From now on‐
I'll tell you where
I'm shooting you.
First, your right thigh.
AHHH!
(pained panting)
Next, your left arm.
Ugh!
H‐how...?
(laughs)
Kirihara:
Well, well. I'll bet The Worst
One feels pretty stupid
right now‐ doesn't he?
I'll bet you thought
I couldn't get any better!
My Area Invisible can
make the arrows I shoot
invisible too, now!
That means you won't see
them till they hit you!
You got that,
dumbass?!
Left hand, coming up!
Ahh!
Look at that!
Hangetsu:
Kirihara shows us some
devastating new tricks!
This is bad...
It is...
Big Brother's
strategy...
has been foiled
completely.
Kirihara:
Left thigh‐ order up!
Why didn't he make a move
right at the beginning?
Huh?
Stella:
He knew his enemy was
going to disappear.
He could've ended this fight
before it even started!
Shizuku:
But... his technique requires
that he study his opponent...
All he's doing
is wasting himself...
fending off
invisible attacks.
Huh?
Stella:
It should've been an easy
decision for him.
It's not that
he didn't do it...
It's that
he couldn't.
Huh?
It should've been
an easy decision for him,
But he's nervous
as hell...
What do you mean?
That's ridiculous!
He wasn't nervous at all...
Ikki:
Don't worry...
Ah!
I will... defeat him.
Ikki...
he was so sure‐
it did seem
extremely unlike him...
Alice:
Honey‐ when you think about
everything he went through
just to get this chance...
can you imagine any world
in which he wasn't terrified?
Even if he was
acting normal...
it was just
a mask.
Oh my God. There's no way he
wasn't nervous.
False confidence...
just a smoke signal‐ darling.
Why couldn't I see it? I was
the closest person to him...
Kirihara:
Get it together, Worst One.
Your graduation is
on the line, isn't it?
The new director didn't do you
any favors...
with your special
graduation requirement...
Huh? What is he
talking about?
Only he has a requirement
for graduation?
Kirihara:
Left elbow next!
Winning at the Seven Star
is the only way
you're gonna be able to
graduate, isn't it?!
He thinks he can win
at Seven Star?
He's out of his mind!
He's Rank F, isn't he?
Is he serious?
(laughter)
Oh no, they're
all laughing at you.
Aren't you mortified?
Hey, why don't you declare
right here in front of everyone
that you're gonna win
at the Seven Star?
Hah! He's miserable.
A Rank F talking
about winning? Impossible.
Just because he beat Rank A
by sheer dumb luck.
Male Student 1:
There's a rumor that
the match was fixed.
Male Student 2:
Once a Rank F‐
always a Rank F.
All these people who don't
know what real courage is...
and they're making
fun of him...
Kirihara:
Lets try something vital
this time...
(arrow impacts)
Kirihara:
(cackles)
Everyone. Kurogane
is discouraged‐
so let's cheer him up!
For the Worst One‐
let's hear it!
For the Worst One!
The Worst One!
Students:
Kirihara:
The Worst One!
Students:
Kirihara:
Come on!
Students:
The Worst One!
Kirihara:
Come on!
Students:
The Worst One!
SHUT UP!
Stella:
He's better than all of you...
you stupid bastards!
Ikki! Don't you ever
look like that!
Don't you ever
let me see you giving up!
I like you better when you're...
when you're looking up!
Show me your strength!
You better show me your strength
at all times‐ you dumbass!
(sighs)
Thank you, Stella.
Just what I needed.
(cackles)
Being scolded by a girl
pepped you up huh?
Stop being arrogant,
Ikki Kurogane.
You've been fixated
on seeing his arrows...
Well I guess... I'll aim
for your broken little
brain this time.
And then
you'll be dead!
There was only
one way...
one way from
the beginning...
Alright... Itto Shura!
Let's see you
avoid this, loser!
Remember... the
sequence of his shots...
the timing...
Here it comes!
(cackles)
The depths, the angles...
Kirihara:
I'm gonna gitchya!
Remember his taunts...
their proximity...
Time for you to die!
Remember his taunts...
their proximity...
Time for you to die!
Huh?!
That's what I thought.
Now I know... where you're
coming from‐ Kirihara.
Huh? No way!
You can see it?!
I can't see your shape
or shadow... But I know.
Kirihara:
That is impossible!
Ahh!
Your rhythm...
your level of
emotion...
Even the depth of
pain you inflict...
They're giving me
everything I need....
I can trace them all back...
to... their source...
That's where I
find you... hiding!
I see you...
You can't hide from
me anymore!
(laughter)
Look at that!
This kid really is
full of surprises!
But how... how did he
do it‐ Miss Saikyo?
How was Kurogane
able to find Kirihara?
With his "Blade Steal."
Nene:
Kurogane can use it
to observe, adopt,
and even perfect his
opponent's technique...
He just used an advanced version
of it to read, anticipate
and pre‐empt Kirihara's
very thoughts.
That version's called...
"Perfect Vision"...
I can see
everything.
Kirihara:
HE'S CHEATING!
Are you ready,
Kirihara...?
With all of my
strength...
I will defeat
all of yours!
Kirihara:
(frantic screams)
Million Rain!
Wait, wait! Stop!
Stop it!
Stop it, please!
Don't!
I know, let's play rock,
paper, scissors!
Kirihara:
Can we just be friends?!
That sword could
kill me! Come on!
WE'RE FRIENDS! Come on man
I'm begging you!
CONCEDE!
I concede!
I GIVE UUUUUUUUP!
Aaah...
Guess I was one
millimeter off.
Gotta work
on that.
Shizuya Kirihara
has conceded the match.
The winner is
Ikki Kurogane!
Hangetsu:
An F‐Rank knight who
couldn't even take classes
last year steps up!
His very first official match‐
a stunning victory!
He did it!
(sighs)
Big Brother...
Students:
(stunned chatter)
Huh? Oh!
Stella:
Ikki!
Hangetsu:
Medical! Medical
to the field please!
We have to get Kurogane
to an IPS capsule!
(chuckles) Somehow I
just knew I couldn't miss
this year's selection matches.
Uhh...
Hm?
Stella:
(snoring)
Heh.
Hiya, sweetheart.
Aren't you gonna go in?
(sighs)
Huh?
We can stay here
for a little while...
I've got
you now...
(whimpers)
Stella:
Noooo!
I can't believe you kept
looking at me while I drooled!
You... ASS!
Oh! I'll just bet it was real
funny wasn't it, you piece of...
Whoa, Stella, take it easy!
Oh! I'll just bet it was real
funny wasn't it, you piece of...
How could you?!
How could you let that little
prick beat up on you like that?!
I'm really sorry...
I keep embarrassing
myself...
Sorry to
make you worry.
I‐I wasn't worried
about you‐ you dumbass!
Stella.
Huh?
I really...
I really like you...
Huh?!
I'm very lucky...
to have met you...
I‐ what the
hell are you‐
what are you
talking about?
Uh... When I said
that I liked you before...
...what I meant was your way of
life and your aspiration,
that kind of stuff.
Yeah I know...
But I... I just wanted
to tell you the whole truth.
No fair.
What?
It's no fair‐ you being all
honest and everything...
Now close your eyes!
Uh, are you...
gonna hit me?
Just shut up and
close your damn eyes!
I... I... whatever
you say....
D‐Don't you misunderstand me.
I did that cuz... well,
I did it because I... wanted to.
Does that mean...
that you... like me back?
Mm‐hmm.
Whoa!
Hmm.
I'm gonna let you get
away with that...
because you're injured.
Ikki:
Stella...
When you're
with me...
I feel like I could
do anything...
Stay with me.
We'll make each other the
best of knights. And then...
In the final battle
for the top position...
It'll just be
you and me.
Careful with that wish...
because I am not going
to lose to you again.
Stella & Ikki:
It's a promise.