(battle cry)
(swords swinging)
(dodging)
(swords clash)
(battle cry)
(clash)
Nice!
Okay‐ Let's
call it quits for now.
(intetsu dissipates)
(relieved sigh)
That was
a good bout!
So did you get your
first battle yet?
Yeah‐ I just got
the email from ad‐min.
I'm fighting Momotani‐
he's a junior.
Oh...
Yeah‐ I've seen him
in a fight before.
His device is a
rare armor‐type, and...
Stop right there.
I do not want to hear
another word about it‐
thank you very much.
You don't‐ really?
Nope!
I don't wanna
know a thing...
Battles like this are supposed
to be training for the future...
when I end up fighting
blazers I've never met.
Ikki:
I see.
And of course you won't always
know what their abilities are...
Exactly!
I also think it's important
to research your opponent
[just] like you do.
(chuckles)
Mm...
What's so funny?
It's just strange...
You and I are so
different...
but we get along
really well.
O‐oh...
Mm!
Uh...
(nervous laugh)
(school bell rings)
First bell...
let's go.
Huh? Oh... ahh!
Uh...
(frustrated growl)
Ikki!
Huh?
Isn't umm...
isn't it Friday today?
Yeah.
So that means...
tomorrow is Saturday
and the school is out...?
That's right.
Oh, okay... so...
SO... MAYBE YOU
AND I COULD...
Uh... I mean...
umm...
We could...
Uhh... could
go an a d...
Aaah!
(cell phone ringing)
Oh! I'm sorry‐ that's me...
Is it about
your opponent?
(cell phone beeps)
Is it about
your opponent?
Stella & Ikki:
Oh...
SHIZUKU!
(cell phone beeping)
Huh?
"Okay... I will see...
you then..." and send.
Oooh.... ahhhh!
Stella:
OH, COME ON!
Ikki:
Huh? What? what?!
(giggles)
(pouty snarl)
This is such
a surprise!
Who would ever have imagined
that such a noble and refined
princess as Her Highness...
would deign to join my
brother and me for our
private leisure...
When I told him I wanted
to learn more about Japan‐
he invited me
to tag along...
He is a gracious
master‐ MY Ikki.
(embarrassed laugh)
Perhaps it would
be wise‐ Princess...
for you to go back home
and practice reading
between the lines.
Oh‐ I can read
between these lines.
And I will not allow my
master to endanger himself
by being alone with
his freakishly obsessive sister.
Hmph!
Hi‐ uh... We haven't
been introduced...
Shizuku asked me
to accompany her.
I am her new roommate.
Nagi Arisuin.
Just all
me Alice.
Alice?
Oh, my!
Did I just get
a "once‐over"?
You are going to be
trouble, aren't you?
Mmm...
Oh, sorry.
But, I mean...
you're a guy‐ aren't you?
Mmm...
Well‐ clinically,
I suppose...
Mmm...
But rest assured....
I've the heart
of a maiden.
Mmm...!
Well‐ I... I don't know what I'm
supposed to rest assured of...
Mmm...!
(chuckles)
You are adorably
serious...
You know... I think
that's wonderful.
Maybe I should try
to seduce you...
Ooh!
(glass breaks)
(splash)
Mmm...
Just joking!
Just a joke!
You can stand
down, honey!
Shizuku! Put that away‐
you're going to get in trouble!
(train rolling)
Wow! The shopping
malls here are amazing!
Shizuku, you're pretty dressed
up for the mall today, aren't
you?
Yes!.. Alice coordinated
this whole outfit for me!
Huh?!
Oh.My.God,
Shizuku!
Stop holding
your brother's hand!
What's wrong
with that?
It's a perfectly ordinary
show of affection
between siblings.
My big brother...
has always held my hand when
we're walking... haven't you?
(laughs)
Yeah, I suppose I have.
Well... then I guess
I should too...
Shizuku:
Really?
Huh?
Doesn't that
seem like it's a little
inappropriate
for a servant?
Ugh...
But, of course...
if he allows
it‐ it's all right.
Oh but... a simple servant
holding her master's hand...
seems to indicate some very
un‐servant‐like feelings.
OH MY IS IT POSSIBLE?!
(embarrassed growl)
NO, IT IS NOT POSSIBLE!
HE IS MY MASTER!
And I'm simply his servant.
Then you have no reason
to hold his hand, do you? Hmph.
So, my big brother,
shall we go?
Uh, yeah...
Shizuku:
Oooh, I know! Let's go
get something to eat!
(growls)
Ikki:
I could go
for anything...
(growls)
Then please
go for me!
(growls)
The food court's
this way...
(pouty grunt)
Stupid Ikki!
You pervert!
You idiot! Such a stupid...
perverted... idiotic...So gross!
THERE we go now...
Let it all out, honey...
You idiot! Such a stupid...
perverted... idiotic...So gross!
Hey, man. You about ready
to switch out?
Oh yeah, She's all
yours. Great...!
(door kicked)
Huh!
Wow! This stuff is delicious!
(noms)
Mmmm!
I know‐ isn't it?
The cream is so rich
and still so delicate...
Well good!
This place is such
a lovely little gem,
I'm glad
you like it!
Although,
for ice cream,
might I recommend a spot
up on the third floor...?
You seem to know
a lot of places...
When it comes to delicious
sweets and keen fashion sense...
no one in the world can
beat my roommate... Right?
Alice:
(chuckles)
It's what I live for.
Oh, Shizuku.
Huh?
Oh...! Huh?
Stella:
Ah!
Don't want to get anything on
your pretty dress, do you ?
Oh...!
Ikki:
There ya go.
Oh my.
I guess there's no
defensive power you can use
against that‐ is there?
Oh shut up, Alice!
It's not a big deal‐
Shizuku:
he just took me by
surprise is all‐
I wasn't expecting him
to reach out and...
Huh? Ooh!
What? Oh hey‐ do I have
something on my face?
How does that happen
without you even noticing?!
Well‐ if there's
anything on my face,
you can just
take it off
like you did
for your sister, right?
Yeah but... this is
a whole different level...
I'm gonna go
find you a towel...
Ahh!
Stella:
No‐ wait, Ikki!
Miss Stella...
Were you dropped on
your head a lot as a child?
(chuckles) Oh honey‐
you are just precious!
Alice:
I mean it‐ I am
rooting for you.
Oh just... Shut up. Hmph!
(footsteps)
(water running)
I have to say‐
I'm surprised.
Shizuku doesn't... well‐
she doesn't open up very easily.
Doesn't she? Well that
isn't such a surprise.
She's very sensitive... and
usually shy around new people.
Ikki:
Especially men.
Alice:
Darling, I am no man.
Heh... Well, I know that
you're a good friend you...
obviously mean a
lot to her. Thank you.
Uh? Heh...
And you are exactly as your
sister describes you.
Very strong,
and exceedingly kind...
However...
That is exactly why you...
Huh?
Oh, don't mind me.
Shall we‐ then?
(footsteps)
Uh...
What's wrong... Mmm!
Yakin:
Man, what a
pain in the ass...
Thug:
It's Bisho's order.
We gotta do it right.
Yeah I know... but damn!
So what if there are a couple of
dudes hiding in here?!
(gunshots)
(glass shattering)
Cool it! Knock it off!
The boss told us to take
anybody we found hostage!
Yeah...
I hear ya, man!
But check it out...!
Yakin:
We just found out
there was no one in here!
Thug:
Jesus...
(door closes)
Who are these people?
Well at the very least‐
we know they're not friendly.
It's possible
that by now...
They've taken
the mall...
Exactly.
Wanna go find out?
I've never seen
your device before...
Well...
Alice:
Meet the Hermit of Darkness.
I can control
shadows with this.
And I can also
use shadows to travel.
Alice:
Let's go. I'm worried
about the girls.
Ikki:
Yeah...
Stella...
Shizuku...
(relieved sigh)
They'll be all right‐
they've just been anesthetized.
Really... It's already
on the news?
Kurono:
Yes. Someone escaped
and called the police.
They've already got
the mall surrounded.
Ikki:
Do we know
who these guys are?
A crime organization led
by a rogue blazer...
They've asked for
an insane ransom...
Ikki:
(sigh)
If money is what they want,
there's gotta be an easier
way than this...
Kurono:
It's not about the money.
It never is with guys like this.
These cowards want to control
people... by making them afraid.
The police have requested
our assistance.
I'm giving the four of you
special authorization
off of school grounds...
to utilize your devices.
(computer beeping)
We won't let
you down... Director.
Kurono:
I'm counting on you...
don't be reckless.
Right!
Yakin:
Hey you! C'mere.
They're taking women
and children hostage...
They're despicable.
I have a plan,
but I need some time...
Whatever you do
don't attract attention
until I'm ready,
all right?
I'll do my best.
Mother:
Please‐ I'm begging you!
Just don't hurt
my child, please!
Get back on your knees
and shut up‐ bitch!
Uhh!
Child:
Don't hurt my mommy!
(struggles)
Stupid little shit!
Uhh!
Momma shoulda taught
you manners‐ boy.
Mother:
No! NO PLEASE DON'T!
So now I WILL!
(dragon roars)
(bullets singe)
(growls)
(flames dissipate)
Well, shit! We got us
a blazer!
Nice try...
But bullets are not really
effective against my
Empress Dress.
Yeah, We'll see!
I am not going to waste
my time with you...
Where's your boss
hiding tough guy?
You got a mouth on you‐ huh?
Eat lead, bitch!
Hold your fire... Yakin!
Yakin:
(gasp)
Well, well! If it isn't the
second princess of the
Vermillion Empire!
It is an honor
to meet you.
And you must
be the boss.
That is correct.
It's a pleasure to make
your acquaintance.
I am Bisho.
You idiot! Were
my instructions not clear?
You were specifically
told not to touch the hostages!
Boss...
I'm sorry...
But that
little bastard
threw an ice cream
cone at my head!
What?! And for that
you try to shoot the boy?!
Heh...
No...
You have been horribly
affronted, Yakin.
Uh‐Yeah.
Bisho:
But honestly now,
you cannot blame
a child for the failures
of his parents, can you?
(gasp)
Don't you dare!
Punishment
follows crime.
Forgiveness
follows punishment.
That's my Motto.
And this woman...
has been negligent in
disciplining her child...
(panicked breathing)
And for that
you'll die...
Good night, "Mommy."
Serve my will, Laevatein.
Heh, heh...
It's a trap!
But I will burn
right through it!
Judgment Ring!
(gasp)
(sword clangs)
What the...?!
Such strength,
and such speed!
But neither will
help you now...
The real world is big
and scary‐ child!
(explosive impact)
(pained gasp)
(pained groans)
This is my device‐ girl.
It is called "Judgment Ring."
It is the circle of
crime and punishment.
The left ring absorbs
the power of your criminal
attacks upon me...
...and the right ring
releases that power
as punishment.
So... You just hit me...
Stella:
with a reflection of
my own full power...
Ha! I like
this girl!
Bisho:
Such a noble
creature,
to risk her own safety
for the "commoners!"
I respect your
courage, Princess.
So perhaps I'll give you a
chance to save their lives.
How then?
You may take his place,
and beg forgivness from me.
(excited inhale)
AND REMOVE
YOUR CLOTHING!
Bisho:
(cackle)
Son of a bitch!
Stay calm‐ love.
It's not time yet...
(chuckles)
This is awesome!
Yeah take
it all off!
Heh, heh. Looks like our little
princess has nerves of steel.
But let's hurry it up now‐
alright my dear?
Ikki:
(frustrated breathing)
(sword clanging)
Alice:
Shadow Bind.
I've held you by your
own shadow... I'm sorry.
Alice...
let me go!
Shizuku's facility with magic
is the best in school.
You must trust
your sister.
Alice:
While Stella has had
them distracted,
she's been creating
a magical barrier.
SHOHA SUIREN!
(water falling)
Bisho:
Shit! There's another
blazer in here!
All bets are off now, boys‐
kill 'em all! Do it!
Yee‐haw!
I leave the rest
to you now... Big Brother.
Ikki:
Come to me, Intetsu.
Christ...
they're everywhere.
Itto Shura.
Right now, I don't
need to see in color.
I'll repurpose
those receptors...
...to see only
what is necessary.
Ikki:
If I attack him
on his left...
he'll turn it
against me...
RIGHT THEN!
(blood gushing)
Seventh Secret Sword. Raiko!
(whailing in pain)
If my sword is faster
than your "judgment,"
then you cannot use
it against me.
You took... my hand!
You should consider yourself
very fortunate...
that's the
only thing I took.
YOU...
BASTARD...!
I think... your little
show is over‐ honey.
YOU THINK SO HUH? BOYS!
KILL 'EM ALL! DO IT NOW!
Huh?
Mm.
Alice:
Oh look! They're all so much
cuter when they're sleeping.
Ikki:
Stella! Stella!
What... I... Oh, my Goodness...
what's wrong, Ikki?
Ikki:
I'm sorry.
I'm so sorry!
Ikki...
Well good Lord...
That was awfully
hasty of you...
running into the middle
of a fight like that.
Although... it was also
decidedly badass...
You too.
You protected everyone...
Heh. Ugh...
Ikki!
Oh, Big Brother!
I'm alright... I'm just
a little drained...
Woman:
(screaming)
Female thug:
Nobody move!... If you
do anything stupid...
I'll kill her.
Is she
one of them?
You are not the only ones
smart enough to hide yourselves
among the
hostages.
You poor
fools!
Female thug:
Listen up! You better
let Bisho go...
Or the bitch dies!
Please, no!
Someone help me!
Pierce them... Oborozuki!
(pained cry)
Uh... ahh!
What...
the hell...?
Where did
that come from?
(chuckles)
Kirihara:
I didn't want to
steal your thunder.
That's really not
my style at all.
Flawless camouflage,
I couldn't even sense him...
That's Kirihara...
It's been a while,
Mister Ikki Kurogane...
The faculty actually
let you stay?
(chuckles)
(sirens wailing)
Female Student:
Oh, Kirihara! We were
so worried about you!
Ha, ha, ha... I wasn't
in THAT much danger.
But you went and beat
the bad guys, right?
You're sooo
awesome!
Ohmygod I KNOW!
Nope... I really
don't like him.
AT least you and I completely
agree about something.
Girls:
(giggling and fawning)
What's up?
Look Kirihara...
Thank you for earlier.
You saved us.
Hey man‐ I'm always happy to
lend a hand to the weak...
Ugh...
So now tell
me something...
Kurogane... are you still
trying to be a magical knight
with that lame
power of yours?
Oh shut up! How about
I shove that smug...
Stella!
It's fine.
Mm.
It's not fine!
You arrogant
little prick!
Ikki is ten times the knight
you could ever hope to be!
(growing laughter)
Uh... what... SHUT UP!
Oh this is
funny!
Sounds like you've got
'em all wrapped around your
little finger‐ Kurogane!
But don't you think you should
tell them all the truth?
Kirihara:
You know... about how
you turned tail and ran on me
because you didn't want the ass
kicking I was gonna give you?
Oh by the way...
you should check your inbox.
Huh?
(cell phone beeps)
Uh!
Yeah... guess who's gonna
be your first opponent...
The guy who's already
represented Hagun
at the Seven Star...
Shizuya Kirihara.
You gonna stick around for the
fight this time, Worst One...?
(seething)