Ikki:
So... what was it
you needed?
Ayase:
Well, the reason I wanted you
to meet me here so late is...
because I have something
important to ask you.
Whatever you need...
I recently heard that you
and Princess Stella...
have promised that you
would fight one another...
at the Seven Star
Sword Art Festival.
That's right.
Ikki:
We both promised
each other...
that we would be
sure to fight again.
I see...
But what if before
you get there...
you're forced to face an enemy
that you can never even hope
to defeat in your life?
What do you think
you'd do then‐ Ikki?
I would fight fair‐
and with everything I've got.
Even if it's hopeless?
Yes. All I can ever do...
is give it all I've got.
Oh no...
there's much more...
You wanna face your enemy
on the higher ground...
you wanna fight fair.
But me...
No matter how much it takes...
I will take him out.
(bell rings)
(blade cuts through metal)
Ikki:
AYATSUJI NOOOOOOO!
Itto Shura!
HAAAAA!
Still not clear...
(swings foot)
(explosion)
I don't understand...
Ayatsuji...
If I hadn't saved
you, you'd be‐
You used it.
You used it!
Itto Shura...
You mean you...
So it was...
your intention from the
beginning to make me use it...?
Ayase:
Your ace
in the hole...
which you can only
use once a day...
The selection match
begins in 10 hours.
You won't have enough
time to recover.
This way‐ I have
a chance to win.
I may not be a skilled
enough swordsman...
but if I combine it with my
ability as a blazer,
I can defeat you now that
you've lost your "ace."
Ikki:
Why...?
Ayase...?
Why is winning
so important to you...?
That you would throw away...
everything the knighthood
stands for...
you'd sacrifice your pride...?
Why would
you do that...?
I do not care
what you say.
I'll defeat you
however I can...
because I have to.
(pants)
W‐wait.
Ayase...
please wait...
Oh... oh...!
No you don't, Ikki...
We can't out here...
Not "Nighttime Itto Shura..."
But everybody is looking at us.
(giggles)
I told you no Ikki!
(thud)
I can't... what was...?
Ikki?
Oh my God, Ikki‐ what are you
doing?! It's the middle of the
night!
What the...?
Well are you gonna
say something‐ or uh... uh...?
Oh! Wait I've heard about this!
You Japanese guys...
get... sneaky... when the lights
go down...? Uh...
Hey... Ikki...?
Ikki what are... uh...
Ikki? IKKI WAKE UP!!!
Uh... where am I?
Shizuku:
Big Brother!
Ikki:
Shizuku...
Oh thank God...
Are you alright?
How long was I...?
Ahh!
Stella:
You still have time.
The match doesn't
start until 3pm.
So you still have
plenty of time.
Alice told us.
Ayase Ayatsuji wanted
to meet you last night.
Yeah...
She was...
Oh good, it looks like you're
finally awake, Kurogane.
I know you must be tired...
but I need you for a sec...
Male Student:
What the heck
was this...?!
Male Student:
What the heck
was this...?!
Kurono:
So... I think
I recognize your work,
Mr. Kurogane.
I heard you were brought
into the Nurse's Office,
so I had what we
call "a hunch..."
I can't
say anything.
But I will accept the
punishment...
Stella:
Ah! Hey, Ikki!
Ikki:
Stella...
(chuckles)
Why now Mister Kurogane... might
you be covering for someone?
Ikki:
May I ask you
something, Director?
Hm?
About Ayase Ayatsuji
of Class 3‐1.
Well‐ he'll find out on his own,
so I might as well...
About two years
ago... I think...
her father, Kaito Ayatsuji,
better known as the
Last Samurai...
wielded his sword
for the very last time.
Well what happened
to him...?
His school was challenged and he
fought a one‐on‐one battle to
defend its honor.
His opponent was‐
The Sword Eater...
from Donro Academy...
Kurashiki... correct?
Kurono:
That's right.
And according to the rules they
agreed upon before their duel,
ownership of the family's
land and holdings was
transferred to Kurashiki.
What about Kaito?
What's his condition?
He's been unconscious...
for the past two years.
Kaito:
Ayase, listen...
A warrior must never lose
sight of her pride.
Value civility.
Help the weak. Hate all evil.
No matter the enemy‐ you face
them fair and square....
Become a
swordswoman of honor.
Ugh!
Kurado:
You know...
You're not even worth the time
it would take me to kill you.
Don't come back.
(seething)
I could fight him at the
Seven Star Sword Art Festival.
It's... my last chance.
I...
I'm... I'm... sorry...
Don't apologize
anymore, Father.
I promise I'll
get everything back.
That's a terrible
story.
Everything the poor girl ever
loved or treasured
was taken from her.
Alice:
But that's what makes her
so fierce.
She's like a desperate
animal.
And she see you as the only
thing that's standing
in her way.
So what are you
gonna do, Ikki?
I'm going to fight her
with all my heart and soul.
Anything less...
would be an insult.
Shizuku:
Okay, but...
She used such
a dirty trick...
Shizuku.
Stella.
Hm?
Would you...
come with me?
Yeah... okay...
to where?
I've just got...
one more thing
that I need to do...
before the
big fight.
Huh?
Hangetsu:
Here we are on
Training Field Three,
and today's third match
is just about to begin!
I'm your reporter...
Hangetsu Tsukuyomi checking in.
On commentary:
Miss Yuri Oriki!
Hello everybody!
Students:
(cheers)
Well Miss Yuri, I must say
you're looking well.
Mmm. Thanks so much‐ but we're
just getting started...
The Miss Yuri you
all know and love
will be back to
her old ways soon.
But don't worry!...
I've got spare blood
and I'm ready to GO...
Bleeeghhhh...
Hangetsu:
Well folks... as Miss Yuri
demonstrates, what's a battle
without bloodshed?!
Female PA:
Combatant entering
via the East Gate.
Hangetsu:
And here's the
First Year Sensation,
an F‐rank knight with
a perfect record
of six wins for
six fights...
We used to call
him "The Worst One"
but now we call him
"Another One..."
Still undefeated...
Ikki Kurogane!
Female PA:
Combatant entering
via the West Gate.
Hangetsu:
Across from him, Combatant
Number Two makes her appearance.
Also undefeated‐ a Third‐Year
with a spotless record
of six wins for six fights...
She is a D‐rank knight
from class three‐one...
Ayase Ayatsuji!
Students:
(cheers and applause)
Kagami:
"Uniquely Gifted Swordsman
and Swordswoman...
Devoted Pupil‐ Ayase
Rises Up Against
Her Swordmaster‐ Kurogane..."
"Student Versus Teacher In An
Epic Battle From which there
Can Emerge Only One Victor..."
Front page!
So you showed up after all.
I was hoping to make this
a "win by default, This time."
I'm really quite
impressed‐ Kurogane.
Come to me, Intetsu.
I know that you will
never forgive me.
But I'm the one who wins.
Come, Blade of scarlet, Hizume!
I don't know
her power...
what kind of a
blazer is she, Alice?
There's almost no
information about her‐
and believe me‐
I've been looking.
She didn't enter any of
the official matches
prior to this year‐
so there's no data anywhere.
She's won every battle this year
with nothing but her sword.
So nobody's seen
her abilities.
That means... whatever kind
of abilities she possesses...
Are a mystery to everyone‐
including Ikki.
Computer:
Let's go ahead.
Whoa! We are off with
a big bang!
Hangetsu:
A swift opener
from Kurogane!
(bell rings)
(slashes through air)
Ugh...
Hangetsu:
What on Earth did we
just see, folks?!
Kurogane takes a severe cut
in mid‐air!
And Ayatsuji didn't
even appear to move!
Kurogane is staggered by a
mysterious attack...
Trying to recover from what had
to be a devastating blow!
(bell rings)
Ahh! Nngh...
Hangetsu:
Oh! An attack from behind?!
Big Brother‐ No!
My Noble Art...
"Mark of the Wind."
What do you think of it?
It does seem...
pretty effective...
Cutting you with the Mark of the
Wind...
That's the ability of my
device, Hizume.
I think... she's placing traps
somehow with her device...
Then triggering them
when I pass through...
Ayase:
I made plenty of cuts in the air
before we got here.
All I have to do
is activate whichever one
is closest to him...
and a vacuum blade
releases a whirlwind attack.
Ikki:
Then she's already pre‐loaded
the entire field...
With enough sword‐slices to
cut him to shreds.
There's nowhere you can run!
If she is planting these traps
before the match...
that is industrious‐
but it's illegal...
If that's what she did‐
they're gonna figure it out...
the match will be forfeit...
and my Big Brother will win...
Ayase:
Good. Yuri hasn't noticed yet.
How about Kurogane?
Not yet.
What the...?!
Is he figuring out my traps?
He can't be sure yet.
So before he is...
(bell rings)
Gah... Ahh!
Hangetsu:
Another hit! And Kurogane
is brought to his knees!
But we still haven't
seen the attack!
It looks as though these wounds
are opening all by themselves!
Ikki:
That was...
also her...
I used my ability
to open that wound.
Using that tiny cut I made with
Hizume just a moment before.
I've got him...!
If she hits me
in the wrong place,
I could wind up
dead out here!
And Ayatsuji unleashes an
aggressive assault...!
Hangetsu:
putting Kurogane
on the defensive!
Kurogane...
I'm sorry...
Big Brother!
You tricked me!
His "irregular
guarding" technique!
She can't
beat it!
He is more impregnable‐
the closer you get...
That's true...
Ikki:
Good.
I'm happy to
see that...
that you really are
who I thought you were.
Huh?
Yuri:
What is it I can do
for you, Mr. Kurogane?
Ikki:
Ma'am...
Miss Yuri...
I think that Miss Ayatsuji
is going to break the rules....
Bleeeeeghhhhh!
Are you sure?
Then... as soon as we
spot it we can stop
the match immediately.
No.
Then... as soon as we
spot it we can stop
the match immediately.
Please don't. I'd like for
you to overlook the violation.
Bleeeeeghhhhh!
What?! Why, Ikki?
If Miss Ayatsuji really
is violating a rule,
then the match will
be forfeit and you'll be
declared the winner.
You're perfectly aware how
important each selection match
is, aren't you‐ Mr. Kurogoane?
Ikki:
Yes...
If I lose even
one match...
I probably won't be going
to the Seven Star...
Yuri:
And even so,
you want...
Yes Miss Yuri.
I do.
Can you at least
tell me why Ikki?
I wanna believe.
...to believe...
what...?
If I end my friendship
with Ayatsuji...
that would be just
like losing the match.
Is beating her
that important?
I've thought about
it a lot lately
and I still don't
have an answer.
But... I can answer
something else...
And what is that?
I know... that a really good
friend can be hard to find...
and we have
to hold on to them.
(sighs)
(giggles)
Miss Yuri... can you please
give me one last chance...
to find out
what she really wants?
Ayatsuji.
Now‐ your
swordsmanship...
your steps‐ and
your breathing...
They're all out of order.
Not only what I taught you...
you're not even using your
former technique effectively.
You're trying to create
something dark inside you...
But you can't fool your soul.
When your mind is lost,
You can't meet your potential.
Shut up Kurogane!
Ayatsuji.
There is so much more
to you than this.
Your pride is true...
I can see it in your father's
technique... Ayatsuji Itto‐ryu.
But my mind
is not lost!
I learned the hard way
two years ago...
no matter how much pride
you have in yourself...
it does you no good
at all if you lose.
Pride without strength to back
it up... its meaningless!
So I'll do
whatever it takes!
I will beat you
no matter what...
AND get back
what I lost!
Then there's only one thing
that I can do for you.
Ayatsuji... with all
of my strength...
I will bring back
your pride!
I will WIN!
Ayase... prepare yourself!
Hangetsu:
Kurogane is dashing towards her!
But this is not
Itto Shura!
He doesn't seem to be using
any powers at all!
(bell rings)
Ayase:
He's using his Perfect Vision.
I knew he had it.
I need to be faster...
faster than
his eyes can be...
Or I'll never defeat
the Sword Eater.
I can't lose.
I cannot give up yet!
Not yet.
This isn't over!
The Fourth Secret
Sword... Shinkiro.
Hangetsu:
He's done it!
Kurogane took her down
with one clean swing!
Well he did it...
but what...?
Right before
he cut her...
he must've switched his
device into phantom form.
Why would he do
something like that?
From the beginning‐
his intention was
to drain her energy.
'Cause his objective...
wasn't just to win the match.
Damn you...
you're holding back!
Yes... I am.
I don't have to hurt you
to beat you now.
Don't insult me!
(struggling)
There's no way I'm done
fighting with you yet...
Why can't I move?!
Why?! Why...?
When we're on the edge,
and have nowhere to go...
The only thing that
can support us...
is the pride we have
in our swords.
What's happened
to yours?
Where have you
hidden it Ayase?
It's gone...
I see...
I can see it now...
I've been deceiving myself
this whole time...
I guess you were right
about me, Ikki.
So I lose...
I'm done.
Hangetsu:
There we have it! Ayase Ayatsuji
has conceded the match!
And another one bites
"Another One's" dust!
Kurogane wins again!
I am so pathetic.
I fought like a coward... and I
couldn't even see that through.
You're not
pathetic, Ayase...
You got hurt, made mistakes,
lost sight...
But you never threw away your
father's Ayatsuji Itto‐ryu.
And that's where your
strength comes from.
(whimpers)
Ayase... I want
to help you...
to get back
what you lost...
I want us
to be friends...
Why, Ikki...?
How could you...?
After everything
I've done to you...?
So why would you? What reason
could you possibly have?
I'm your friend.
And I don't need a reason...
to help a friend.
I only...
wanted...
to become... the kind of
swordsman that my father was.
I'm sorry Ikki...
(sobbing)
I'm sorry...
Please help me...
I can't do it alone.
Then the two of us
will do it together.