Shizuku:
It took too long for me
to really see it...
the cruelty that we
can hide away...
behind a mask
of peace.
And how this person
that I love...
how he'd been forced
to suffer.
Father, mother,
the whole family...
none of them
ever loved him.
They hurt him.
And now they only want
to hurt him even more.
But if that's what they
want, then I...
(panting)
(drinking water)
Good run‐
Miss Stella.
(panting)
Just Stella!
Oh...
Yeah right...
just Stella...
We done?
I usually run about
20 kilometers every day...
You know‐ you don't
really have to‐
I'm fine‐
this is nothing.
And besides...
you have very powerful magic
that can compensate
for a lack of‐
LACK OF WHAT?!
Did I or did I not finish?
(winded sigh)
Man, you've got a competitive
streak don'tcha...?
Here.
Uh... what are you...?
Uh... you need
your electrolytes...
You drank from...
It'd be like
kissing you...
Oh‐ right!
You don't wanna drink out of
that‐ it's got my germs on it!
Sorry.
What? When did I
say anything about germs.
Maybe I want those germs...
What?
WHAT? NEVER MIND!
I need my electrolytes!
(water sloshing in bottle)
(drinking)
Huh?
Look how happy you are!
Yeah, my sister starts
school here today...
four years since
I've seen her...
Oh!
So she's your sister?
That's like a real
sister‐ right?‐
not like a friend
you call "sister..."?
Yup. As in "daughter
of my mother and father."
I'll allow it.
Ikki:
Okay, well...
thank you...?
Helloooooo freshmen!
Welcome to you all!
I'm your teacher,
Yuri Oriki!
I'm new too‐ you guys
are my very first class‐
so you can all just
call me Miss Yuri.
Now we won't have class today,
She looks like she
hasn't slept in a year.
but I do have one thing to add
about the selection match
(laughs) I know,
but she's a good teacher.
but I do have one thing to add
about the selection match
(laughs) I know,
but she's a good teacher.
for the Seven Star
Sword Art Festival.
Of course, I'm sure all of you
remember very well
what the Director said
during assembly...
Kurono:
Traditionally‐ Hagun Academy's
representatives have been chosen
based on score.
this year, students will face
one another in battle
to determine our top six.
Our team of representatives....
will be composed
of these six students.
Kurono:
This year's selections...
will be simple and fair.
Yuri:
So‐ I'm sure I don't have to
remind you that the school match
will start next week!
You'll be informed of your
fight schedule and opponent
by emails to your student ID.
Professor...?
No, no! Call me Miss Yuri,
or I won't answer your question!
Stella:
Uh...
M‐Miss Yuri...?
Yes? Your question,
Miss Stella?
How many matches
will we be fighting?
Yuri:
It could easily amount to more
than 10 matches per student.
It's safe to assume
that you'll be fighting a match
once every three days.
Male Student:
Whoa, seriously?
Female Student:
That's insane!
I don't even care about the
Seven Star Bored Fart Festival!
Once every three days.
Female Student:
I don't even care about the
Seven Star Bored Fart Festival!
In that case, maybe I can
use Itto Shura.
Yuri:
If you don't wish
to participate then don't...
Doing so will in
no way affect your grades.
But in my opinion,
you're all being given
a really wonderful opportunity
to compete with one another
on a level playing field...
And so... I do hope
you'll all try.
Okay guys!
This coming year...
let's all do
our very best!
AAAALLLLLright
let's give a cheer!
Hip, hip hoorAGGGHHHH!
(students screaming)
(concerned gasp)
Miss Yuri!
(sigh)
There she goes...
Yuri:
No reason to worry.
To tell the truth‐
I vomit at least
a liter of blood per day...
(coughing)
Th‐That's awful...
You shouldn't push yourself
so hard‐ Miss Yuri...
Mm. Oh I know,
but it's a big day!
I just wanted to be
at my very best for you guys...
Miss Yuri got
me accepted here.
I'm only in this school
because of her...
No Ikki.
It was nothing but your own
ability that got you in here.
Although‐ last year
was very unfortunate...
(nervous laugh)
Huh?
So... Why was last
year so "unfortunate"?
Oh‐ that's...
just because I wasn't
allowed to take any classes.
There was no standard criteria
for measuring my ability score.
Alright, so
why didn't...
Kagami:
Mister Kuroganeeeeeeeeeee...!
(gasps)
Whoa!
I finally get to meet
you‐ Mister Kurogane!
Omygod whatareyou...
WHO IS THIS?!
I don't have any idea!
Who are you‐ Miss...?
Kagami! Kagami Kusakabe‐
I'm in your class!
I'm such a HUGE fan of yours!
Ikki:
What...? Fan...?
(snarling)
I saw you fight!
In the mock battle!
Amazing‐
Mister Kurogane!
Maybe that's
a stretch...
I'm thinking seriously about
starting a newspaper club.
And I want you to be
on the front page of our
historic first issue!
Would you please let me
interview you?
I really don't think
I'd be much of a...
Well look at you‐ already so
popular from the first day of
the school!
You definitely don't wanna
keep your public waiting‐
"Mister Amazing..."
No... STELLA!
I've already got
the perfect headline!
"Ikki Kurogane:
Genius In Our Midst‐
A Man Nobody
Noticed Before,
Becomes The Center
Of Attention"!
That's... a really long
headline‐
Can we talk later?!
Okay then...
Stella, WAIT!
Well‐ I finally found you!
Uh?
(students talking)
(giggles)
Shizu...ku?
Huh?
Male Student 1:
Dude, that's...
Male Student 2:
Lorelei!
Female Student:
She's second best
of the freshman!
I've really missed you...
my big brother!
Wow‐ Shizuku!
You look different!
I was going to come
searching for you later...
But it seems
like you beat me to it!
I know! I just really
couldn't wait to see you...
Big Brother...
Uh...
(kiss)
Hm?
(gasp)
Oh!
(students in shock)
What the hell is THIS?!
WOW! Front page,
FRONT PAGE!
(pants)
I have missed you...
so much...
Shizuku...?
I‐ I can't even...
IKKI OH MY GOD
WHAT IS HAPPENING HERE?!
I haven't got
the slightest idea!
I'm simply kissing
my beloved brother.
Kissing is only a
show of affection...
If two people who share a bond
like "romantic love" can kiss...
Then why... shouldn't I
be able to kiss my big brother‐
with whom I share such
a rare and special bond?
Besides, it's like a greeting
in foreign countries...
Hm? It is...?
There are NO siblings who kiss
like that in my country!
In any other country,
actually!
I haven't
heard of it...
This is about us. Ignore them
all‐ Big Brother.
We've been
separated for four long years...
even sleeping together at
night...
wrapped in each others arms
wouldn't be strange for us.
YES IT WOULD!
Shizuku! You are a young
woman‐ this isn't right!
Jeez‐ I'm
just kidding!
But hey... I can tell it's
what you really want so...
THAT'S IT!
(struggling)
(yelp)
Pull yourself
together, Ikki!
Don't just sit
there like an idiot!
Uh right, thank you, Stella...
Shizuku:
So you're the famous
Princess Stella...
I'll advise you
not to insert your petty,
common jealousies between
my brother and me...
Stella:
Looks to me like someone
needs to put something
between your
brother and you!
Oh really?
That's for my big brother
and me to decide.
Your opinion means
nothing to us!
Huh!
We're related in ways
some feeble princess
could never
understand.
Oh yeah?‐ Well he and I
are sorta related too...!
Oh? And just what
way is that...?
BECAUSE HE'S MY‐
I mean he's kinda my...
Shizuku:
What is my brother to you...?
(inhale) HE IS MY
GRACIOUS MASTER...
AND I AM HIS
DEVOTED SERVANT!
Students:
(gasp)
No wait‐
hold on Stella!
I told you we should
forget about that...
THIS IS ONE
JUICY SCANDAL!
I can see
the headline...
Kagami:
"MOGAKE:
Struggle In My Arms‐
A bonded princess servant
and her savage roommate
in closed room
for 72 hours.
What is with...
these long headlines?!
Long but accurate!
After you defeated
me in battle,
you did give me
an order...
Stella... you must
sleep in my bed....
NO‐ STOP
THE FLASHBACK!
You know I didn't say
anything like that!
Is this all true?
Er...
Big Brother... I'm asking
you if it's true.
Well, sort of...
I mean in a way
I guess it's true.
But I really...
just meant the bunk bed...
Shizuku:
(giggles)
Because if it is...
if it is true...
(giggles)
I... I don't...
Shizuku what're you...?
Then Big Brother,
I will free you from your
burden this very moment....
Shower me...
Yoi Shigure!
Shizuku!
No‐ you can't...!
Well of course
I can Big Brother!
I'm water
and she's fire.
Water will always
put out a fire...
Ikki:
No‐ what?‐ that's not
what I'm talking about!
If you use your device
in an undesignated area...
Stella:
Serve my will,
Laevatein.
AND YOU SHOULD
NOT BE ENCOURAGING HER!
(sword swoosh)
It's such a frail and
delicate little device...
It's an awful
lot like its wielder...
Yours seems fitting....
Tasteless, classless,
gilded, gaudy, and provincial.
And of course,
comically oversized....
Well, well, well...
someone seems a little hung up
on the size of my assets‐
maybe she's jealous...
Fat.
Ugly.
(scoffs)
Stella & Shizuku:
NO YOU DID NOT!
(explosion)
Students:
Whoa!
(explosion)
Kurono:
On or off campus,
the activation of devices
outside of a designated
combat area is forbidden.
Ordinarily‐ you'd both
be suspended...
However‐ since it
was the first day‐
you'll just be cleaning
restrooms for a week.
You may now thank me
for my generosity...
Thank you very much for
your generosity‐ Director...
I'm very sorry‐ I promise
to never do that again...
Very good.
You may go home after you've
finished all the ladies'
restrooms in the school.
Don't worry girls, only
twenty six more to go.
(giggles)
Washboard.
Top heavy.
Baby Bee Stings.
Floppy Grandma.
Wet rag.
Dud firecracker.
Stella:
(angry grunt) Zero feet
above sea level.
Shizuku:
Mount Everest.
Both:
(angry panting)
Stella:
Under‐inflated
water balloon.
(panting continues)
Shizuku:
Over‐inflated
sex doll!
Hey, alright‐ I'm gonna give
you a break pipsqueak!
Good‐ then you'll
leave him alone?
You'll stay away
from my big brother
for the rest
of your life?
That's not
what I meant!
And I am sorry
to tell you,
but I can't exactly
"stay away."
When we happen
to be roommates!
Ugh. No matter
what excuse you use
to manipulate
your way into his life...
my big brother will
always belong to me.
What are you‐ crazy?!
This is your actual brother
we're talking about here‐
what the hell is
the matter with you?!
This is something that you are
incapable of ever understanding.
What are you
talking about?
What's the
big secret?!
I didn't say...
It's not that it's...
(footsteps)
What is it?
Whatever it might be,
it's useless to talk to you
because you
will not understand!
You're not a Kurogane‐
you'll never...
Oh don't even try playing
the family card on me!
I've got family too!
You have no idea,
princess!
How my brother felt‐
being treated like
he never existed!
Oh.
Uh.
Stella:
What do you mean...
"like he
never existed"?
I don't
understand...
Shizuku:
Of course
you don't.
And you
never will...
Just leave both
of us alone.
(door opens)
Alice:
Enter:...
"the roommate."
(gasps)
I was wondering when
I was going to meet you.
Well come on in‐
and I will call off
the search and rescue.
I'm Nagi Arisuin...
But My friends just
call me "Alice."
Mm.
What does she mean,
"like he never existed"?
Ikki:
Hey, Stella....
Oh.
What are
you doing here?
Oh, I was...
waiting for you...
Huh?
I mean I thought we were
supposed to practice‐
but then you
didn't show...
I figured you might not
feel up to it today...
Sorry bout that.
It's no big deal...
this is for you...
It was in the room.
Ikki:
Oh, thanks.
Ikki...?
(gulping water)
Hm?
Why would your family
want to treat you
like you never
existed?
(spit take)
Oh... oh! Sorry!
Maybe it would've been better
if I'd been a little less direct
asking that question...
Ah... I guess you've
been talking to Shizuku?
Um... well yeah.
Maybe a little....
It's okay, I wanted
to tell you...
I guess this might be
just as good a time as any.
Huh?
Are you sure you want to hear
this? It's kinda depressing...
Hm... mhm.
Ikki:
Have you heard of
a samurai named Ryoma?
Of course I have!
Stella:
He's the hero that led Japan to
victory in the last world war.
Everyone's heard
of Ryoma Kurogane...
Oh....
Right‐yeah‐that's the one
I mean‐ he's my grandfather.
And he's... the kind of man
I want to be.
Ikki:
For generations, the Kurogane
have produced brilliant Blazers.
What they call a
"distinguished legacy."
But I wasn't like
the rest of my family...
I didn't have their gift...
So they decided that I wasn't
worth acknowledging...
...there was never a seat
for me at my family's table...
Then one year... while I
hid away and listened...
I could hear them
at their New Year's party,
and something
in me just broke...
(wind whipping)
I didn't know
where I was going...
But I... I knew that
I had to go...
Somewhere...
(wind whipping)
I suddenly realized I was lost.
And I was freezing.
I think I was ready to die.
but then all I could think of...
was how frustrating it would be
to die like this.
And then...
he was suddenly there‐
standing in front of me.
(footsteps in the snow)
The samurai Ryoma?
Yes. And I remember
every word he said.
I'll never
forget it...
Does it frustrate you kid?
Does it upset you,
to be the weakest one?
That's good,
hold on to that feeling.
Ryoma:
It's proof. That feeling means
that you are not yet ready...
to give up on yourself.
Take it from me, boy.
Your life will be very boring
if you aspire for no more
than to "live within
your means."
You can be anything you want
to be... look at all mankind!
We were... never gifted
with a pair of wings‐
yet we've still
flown to the moon...
He spoke to me
in the simplest terms...
but those words
saved my life.
Hm.
So I decided...
right then that's the kind
of man I would become.
Someday‐ I might meet someone
like I was then...
I want to give them what
my grandfather gave me.
But in order to do that...
I have to be as strong as I can.
Like my grandfather.
So that's why you wanted
to become a knight.
But no one wanted
to teach me anything...
So I did my
practicing alone.
Alone?
(flames crackle)
(panting)
Ikki:
Eventually... I got
accepted to this school.
Ikki:
My family didn't like the idea
that a failure like me
could earn his place among
them as a knight...
So they started
to pressure the school.
Huh?
The standard requirements
to take a class...
those were created by the
former director of the academy.
To prevent me
from graduating.
(breeze blows)
Luckily, the new director
is Kurono Shinguji.
But my family's going to try
to pressure her too...
But even...
even if they do...
You won't give up.
Even if you end up getting
burned... badly...
Stella:
I think I understand
how you feel...
I mean sort've...
I know...
I know you do, Stella.
However, Ikki‐
there is still one thing we're
going to have to correct here...
What's that?
Earlier today...
you accused me of having
a competitive streak.
Oh...
Yeah, I guess
I should correct that...
Okay so... We're
both competitive.
That's more like it!
(giggles)
Shizuku:
I always loved my brother...
because he was kind.
Even after he left the house...
left us... I still loved him.
When I could see how badly
my family had treated him...
I hated them. I despised them
from the bottom of my heart.
And I decided...
Our father's love, our mother's
love, our brothers' love...
all that they
wouldn't give him...
I would give him all
that he deserves myself.
Heh.
Oh, I'm so sorry!
We just met and I'm
talking your ear off...
You don't like people very much‐
do you Shizuku...?
Huh?
Probably always
been uncomfortable
around strangers...
but it sounds like...
your family made
it impossible
for you to be
comfortable with anyone.
Uh...
I get that.
I used to know a "little girl"
who was a lot like you...
Well, obviously you
and I are now going to be
the very best
of friends.
You ever want to
talk about anything‐
you talk to me‐ okay?
Just like a big sister.
'kay!
Stella:
(humming)
(stew stirring)
(humming continues)
Hm?
(water sloshes in bathtub)
Hm.
(water moving)
(relaxed sigh)
Stella:
Ikki, I'm coming in.
Oh sure, go ahead...
Ahh!
(splash)
Ikki:
AHHH!
S‐Stella?!
What?! Ikki‐ why are you
freaking out like that?
I'm not freak‐ I mean
OF COURSE I'm freaking out!
What are you doing?!
Well I...
I thought that maybe
you would like me to come in
and help you wash up...
Ikki:
Huh? W‐why?
Because, you know...
I mean‐ I took a vow
and I am your servant...
And this is one of the many
things that servants do.
So it's my duty
to bathe you. Right?
But you don't have to‐
I didn't ask!
The very best servants
do not have to be asked!
Sit‐ and let
me do my job... now!
Ikki:
B‐But...
Or I could boil you...
Ikki:
Okay...
(soapy rag scrubbing)
Stella:
Hm.
(scrubbing continues)
(gasp)
(fleshy slapping sounds)
(scrubbing continues)
(exerted sigh)
(restrained sigh)
(fleshy slap)
Here... I'll do
your back next.
O...kay.
Hey, um Ikki?
I uh, want to ask
you something...
W‐what?
Do you like looking at girls'
breasts and stuff?
(stammers)
Why are you asking me that?!
Because... when that girl Kagami
was pushing hers against you‐
you seemed happy.
And I noticed...
you've been...
well you've been
looking at mine a lot...
Uh‐Sorry!
You don't have to apologize,
just... tell me the truth...
Mm...
I like them.
'Kay...
(shower drips)
Mm.
(bouncing effect)
Uh... wha‐ what are
you doing with your...
No! Stay still!
Huh?! Whaaa‐?!
Y‐You're not supposed to move!
(flustered gasp)
Uh... 'kay...!
Don't move...
(bikini unfastens)
(bikini falls)
Uhh?!
O‐oh...
(echoing moan effect)
Uhh...!
H‐Hey, Stella, maybe...?
(shrieks)
Don't look at me!
Uh...
OH!
Uh, Stella...!
This, is this‐ are you‐
umm... uh... n‐naked...?
Stella:
(slaps)
(screams)