Reporter:
Stella Vermillion,
second princess of the
Vermillion Empire
is expected to be arriving
in Japan today.
Recently admitted into
"Hagun Academy,"
with the highest recorded
score in the prestigious
Tokyo Chivalry's history,
she's been said to be among
the strongest and most gifted...
(slight crowd uproar)
Reporter:
We're seeing her now...!
Crimson Princess!
Princess Stella!
Your Highness! Tell us
how it feels to be in...
Ikki:
Some people will tell
you that life is unfair.
They'll tell you it's because
what you were born with
is what you end with.
(crowd chatter)
(frustrated sigh)
Kurono:
Well‐ Miss Vermillion,
Welcome to Tokyo.
Thank you‐ Director.
I'm glad to be here.
(car driving off)
Ikki:
Gifted or ungifted.
Your place in the pecking order
is decided for you
the very moment you're born.
We raise the "gifted" up
to places the "ungifted"
are not allowed to reach...
to places they can never
dream of reaching.
(panting)
(sigh)
But does it always
have to be this way?
(wind whipping)
Ryoma:
Does it frustrate you kid?
Does it upset you‐
to be the weakest one?
That's good, hold on
to that feeling.
It's proof. That feeling means
that you are not yet ready...
to give up on yourself.
(jacket whipping)
Come to me, Intetsu!
Blazers:
those who can manifest a weapon
forged from their own soul...
and use it to wield
extraordinary powers...
(sword swinging)
Ikki:
Blazers approved by the
international organization,
are known as
Magical Knights.
I, Ikki Kurogane...
...aspire to be one of them.
Hm?
(footsteps)
(gasp)
Hold on.
I already know
what you're going to say.
I'm not... going to pretend
I didn't see what I just saw...
So how's this?!
I'll get naked...
and we'll call it even!
(frightened suttering)
NOOOOOOOO!
(slap)
Kurono:
As you already know‐
the Hagun Academy
is one of the
highest‐ranked institutions
among all the
chivalry schools in Japan.
At the prestigious
Seven Star Sword Art Festival,
where the strongest of
students compete,
Aspiring Magical Knights
from our school have won
almost every year.
Unfortunately,
over the past few years,
our record has
been slipping.
I accepted the
post of director,
in order to rebuild
this academy.
And on day one...
Kurono:
I have to deal with something
as asinine as a peeping tom...
I... I know...
just an accident, though!
Kurogane‐ you peeked
at a girl with her clothes off,
and then proceeded
to remove your own.
You call this an accident?
Well‐ maybe
fifty‐fifty?
I mean‐ I was really only
trying to... be a gentleman...
I see‐ so you were...
being a gentleman...
Well yeah, I mean I'm not
like a creep or anything...
Well‐ that's
good to hear.
Let's see you
be a gentleman...
(door opens)
Ikki:
(surprised gasp)
Miss Stella Vermillion!
(shocked gasp)
I uh... I'm sorry that
I surprised you earlier.
I swear, I didn't
do it on purpose.
(indignant scoff)
Ikki:
I accept full
responsibility.
I'll take whatever
punishment you see fit.
What is your name?
Um...
My name is Ikki...
How noble
of you Ikki.
There's no need for us
to turn this into an
international incident.
In light of your apology,
I will show you My mercy.
Thank you.
You may now throw yourself
upon your sword.
Eh...?
(innocent giggle)
That's a...
joke... isn't it...?
It's no joke‐ I have
made a great compromise.
Your compromise is
for me to kill myself?!
"Whatever punishment,"
you said!
It's a figure of speech!
And it was an accident!
(offended gasp)
I'm supposed to pay with
my life for such a little thing!
"Such a little..."?!
(angry realization)
Ikki:
I mean‐ so what? So I saw
you in your underwear!
And now what? I have
to disembowel myself...?
Huh?
Uh... I...
Bye, now.
Huh?! Wait, Director...!
Prepare yourself.
You disrespectful,
creepy, crude,
perverted
little commoner...
I will turn you into
ashes all by myself!
(flames rage)
(fire alarm sounds)
Ikki:
(screams)
Wait, Miss Stella!
Calm down!
You snuck into my room,
and defiled me with your eyes.
How dare you!
"Defiled..."?!
(denying whimper)
I saw the look in your eyes as
you were staring at me!
You're not sorry! You liked it
and you're just mocking me!
Yes I saw you...
but it... was...uh...
(growling)
It was because I've never seen
anyone... so beautiful!
Huh?
(fire sprinkler starts)
(magic fireball ithers)
Y‐you know it's very rude
to just come out
and tell a princess
that she's beautiful without
any c‐c‐consideration for...
(groans)
...I mean there
are rules...
What is it?
Well, earlier, you
said "your room..."
But that's
actually my room...
(shocked gasp)
If you think you're
being funny...
Oh, by the way,
I forgot to tell you,
...you two are
going to be roommates...
Starting today.
Stella & Ikki:
HUUUUUH?!
Kurono:
See? It's official.
I have a
question.
Hmmm?
Usually roommates are students
of the same rank, right?
Then why is
Stella with me?
She's a Rank A
and I got flunked.
WHAT? What do you
mean you "got flunked?"
Mhm. I'm a Rank F...
The only superpower I can use is
a minimal physical enhancement.
My magical power... is about
one tenth of the average.
Other ability scores are
also all at the lowest level...
earned him the nickname
"The Worst One."
Kurono:
Literally, he is the weakest
student at this academy.
"The Worst One."
Kurono:
See kids, this is what they
call a "teachable moment."
Kurogane is totally
and completely inferior...
Vermillion is totally
and completely superior...
Sounds perfect,
doesn't it?
That makes
no sense at all.
B‐B‐B‐But what if there's some
sort of accident or something?
Oh? What kind of "accident"
are you thinking of?
Well... I
mean it's...
We have plenty of male & female
pairings on this campus.
You object? You can
always quit the academy.
(catches breath)
(sighs)
Okay fine...
here's how it is.
If you and I are going
to live together...
then I have three
conditions.
Okay...
Stella:
You may not
speak to me.
(groan)
You may not
open your eyes.
(annoyed groan)
You may
not breathe...
(alarmed groan)
If you like, I'll just
fall down dead right now.
If you can stick
with the rules...
you may live
in front of the room.
I can't be
inside the room?!
What, you
can't do it?
Of course not!
At least let me breathe!
No way! You're thinking about
breathing my aroma, pervert!
Then I'll breathe with my mouth!
Nuh‐uh! You just want to taste
the precious air that I breathe,
you little deviant!
I didn't even
think of...!
If you don't like it,
quit the school!
You're freaking
me out!
Alright, let's just
take a breath...
Chivalry is about deciding your
own destiny with your sword.
Isn't it?
So we should let our
abilities do the talking?
Kurono:
Exactly. You can have
a mock battle...
and whoever wins decides
the rules of your room.
Hm. I suppose
that sounds fair.
What do you say,
Miss Stella?
Umm...
You'll have to forgive me
if I'm being blunt...
But how are you‐
a rank "F"‐
going to beat me‐
a rank "A?"
Takes more than "rank"
to decide a battle...
And besides I've really
been practicing a lot!
(pouty sigh)
Alright fine. I'll let you
have your little battle.
Stella:
But if we're gonna do this,
it's not just the
"rules of the room"
that are on the table anymore.
Uh?
The loser will obey the winner
for the rest of his life!
And no matter how
humiliating it is...
Stella:
he will serve his mistress
like a loyal dog!
You might be taking this
a little too far...
That... is... the... deal!
O...kay...?
Very good then.
(catch reactions)
You two had better get ready.
One hour from now,
the mock battle will begin
on Training Field Four!
(intimidating growl)
(confused reaction)
(disgusted reaction)
(nervous laugh)
(birds chirping)
Stella:
(annoyed scoff)
Seriously...
What do I have
to do this for?
"I've really been
practicing a lot," he says.
Stella, my love.
You don't have to put
yourself through all of this...
I do, Mother.
A little nation such as ours has
to have a really strong
Magical Knight.
Stella:
I promise‐ I am going to learn
how to control this power.
And to get there...
I'll do what I have to.
I'm going to crush you...
Ikki Kurogane.
(students talking)
Female Student A:
Look! It's the
Crimson Princess!
Male Student A:
She's a princess
and a genius!
Female Student B:
Can you even imagine
what her life is like?
Female Student C:
Yeah, but why is she gonna...?
Male Student B:
I know, the mock battle?
And the Worst One, to boot.
Kurono:
I was surprised
you said "yes" to this.
Well‐ she's someone
I have to beat eventually.
"Beat her," huh?
I like your optimism...
You said I have to win at the
Seven Star Sword Art Festival.
(sigh)
Because if I win,
I can graduate even though
my ability score is low.
I'll hold
you to that.
Heh.
And she's sure to compete.
So this has to happen.
Ikki:
Whether it's sooner or later.
Oh, I made it!
I just came to turn in an
application, and I
get to see this!
What luck!
Oh...! She's here!
Ikki:
Hi Miss Stella.
You all set?
I heard about you. I heard
your ability score is so low,
you don't even qualify
to take any real combat classes.
Stella:
Maybe it'd be safer for you
if you just stopped trying
to become
a Magical Knight.
Ikki:
You might be right.
Still... I am not
quitting this match.
Are you one of those people
who think hard work
can stand up
against real talent?
Stella:
You're wrong.
That is exactly
what I believe.
(armor clanging)
Damn it... DAMN IT!
Fallen Fighter:
All this hard work, and I'm
still no match for her talent...
Like I don't work hard...
who the hell do you
think you are?
Huh?
Let's get started.
Director? We are ready
and await your command.
Very well then‐
the mock battle will now begin.
Kurono:
As you all know, a mock battle
is a non‐lethal competition.
The purpose is to drain
your opponent's strength.
Weapons are to be deployed
in phantom‐form only.
(main lights shut off)
Come to me, Intetsu.
(magical electricity)
(sword being drawn)
(sword swinging)
Stella:
Serve my will, Laevatein!
(eruption, fire spinning)
(sword swings)
(sword clangs)
(buzzer)
Computer voice:
Let's go ahead!
(fire rising)
(battle cry)
(readies sword)
(loud impact)
You're smart to dodge.
My Dragon Breath
fire burns at...
around 3,000
degrees Celsius!
Taking it head‐on would've
turned you to ashes!
(sword swings)
(fire roars)
(exerting force)
(swords clang)
(explosion)
(footsteps)
(swords clanging)
(exerting force)
Male Student:
Whoa, man...
Nene:
Just what I thought.
Sometimes I can't
believe you, Ku‐chan.
You really should tell me
about these things‐ you know.
You always know it's
happening anyway. Why bother?
(giggle)
That's very true.
But this is quite...
unexpected‐ isn't it?
I never imagined that
Stella Vermillion
would consent to
such a thing...
(exerting force)
(swords clashing)
Is he...?
Stella:
fending me off...?
You're pretty gifted
at running away.
I'm... observing you...
The sword technique
that you've been using...
I see it. Not just your
talent... Your hard work too.
(surprised gasp)
You've got a
pretty good eye...
But the technique
I've been using...
is going to be harder
than that to see through!
No. I already have...
(loud clash)
My technique!
How could you possibly...?
(jumps back)
(swords clash)
How are you...
How are you using my
technique against me?
When I was a kid...
nobody ever wanted
to teach me anything...
So I had to teach myself
how to see!
When you see through the
branches and leaves to the root,
Ikki:
you'll understand
the truth.
And you can overcome!
(rocks crumbling)
Uh!
(sword rattles)
This is my sword technique.
"Blade Steal."
Alright smart guy,
let's see you steal a feint.
(battle cry)
(sword whiffs)
Uh!
(battle cry)
Your swordsmanship
is slipping.
Huh?
(loud clang)
No way!
A wild attack isn't
like you...
and losing control
is a fatal error!
(swords clash)
Huh?
(battle yell)
(sword impacts)
(fire flowing)
Female Student:
Is this it?
Male Student:
How could a
Rank A...?
No, look!
Uh?
(energy flowing)
(sword swinging)
(steps back)
It doesn't look good...
to win like this.
Ikki:
You knew that Intetsu would not
be able to hurt you at all.
And in spite of that,
you chose a sword battle.
Stella:
Yes... so I could beat
you with my sword,
and let everyone
see for themselves
that there's more to
me than just my talent.
But I will admit...
this battle... the only
reason I'll be able to win
was certainly because
of my magic ability.
Stella:
So with the
greatest due respect...
I will defeat you.
It's true...
that I don't have the gift
to be a Magical Knight.
Pierce the blue sky,
Ikki:
But I won't back down.
flame of purgatory!
The vow that
makes me who I am...
will not allow me
to give up on myself.
That's why I thought about it...
what I need to do
Burn it all...!
in order for the weakest
to beat the strongest.
Calusaritio Salamander!
in order for the weakest to beat
the strongest.
Calusaritio Salamander!
And this is it...
Itto Shura!
Where did he... go?
(gasps)
(exerts force)
(whoosh)
Huh? He's gotten faster!
His power is
getting stonger...
Not getting stronger.
I'm just using it
with everything I've got!
You'll still lose!
Impossible!
Concentrating my living energy
into one minute and using it
all.
That's the Noble Art
that I created.
With all my strength I will
defeat all of yours!
(slash)
(magic disperses)
Wha...?
(gasp)
Uh...
(sword clangs)
For a mediocre man
to defeat a genius...
he... must
become... a demon.
That's it!
Kurono:
The winner...
is Ikki Kurogane!
(amazed gasps)
Well!
This year's selection match is
going to be terribly exciting.
(panting)
(birds chirping)
(door opens)
Huh?
Vermillion.
How are you feeling?
You know‐
I'd almost forgotten...
What it's like...
to lose a match like that.
How is he?
To consume all that
power in one minute...
That's something you can
only do once a day.
He used everything he had
to beat you...
and he's in much
rougher shape than you are.
But... you'll be glad to know
he's going to live.
Madame Director...
what's the story with him?
What... story?
Don't play
dumb with me!
Him being a Rank F
doesn't make any sense.
Your rank... is based solely on
your ability as a Blazer...
Kurono:
Your combat skills,
your swordplay‐
your physical prowess,
are not subject
to evaluation.
As it is, our current
system simply can't
make a proper evaluation
of Kurogane.
Yeah... but failing him?
(sighs)
Listen‐ it's all
very complicated...
Or... maybe it's really
not very complicated at all...
One thing
I can say...
...is that life has been
very unfair to Kurogane.
He's had plenty
of reasons to give up,
but he's never stopped
pushing himself to improve.
Kurono:
That's... a man
no "system" can measure.
Princess... I asked
you this morning...
"What made you
want to study abroad?"
In my home country...
I am in a "prison of genius."
I don't have the freedom
to try something and fail...
Princess Vermillion,
I think there's a lot
you can learn from Kurogane.
Kurono:
I have a feeling...
that he will be a valuable
expenditure of your time.
(snoring)
(stirs)
(sheets rustle)
(fleshy impact)
Um... oh...
This is... this is what
a man's back looks like...
(stirs)
(surprised yelp)
Oh! Oh my God!
(Stella struggling)
(bed creaking)
Stella:
Maybe if I could...
I could just... Oh God....
Mm...
(exerts force)
(hand slips free)
(embarrased gasp)
Stella:
(shaky breath)
NO STELLA! You are a princess
and this is totally disgraceful!
But he is so...
(sleeping)
Hang on... this guy
totally walked in on me
and saw me
in my underwear...
Stella:
So this just makes
us even, right...?
(sighs)
This is... what a
man's body feels like...
(ding)
(sparkle)
Oh my God! I've never
felt anything like this...!
(gasp)
(panting)
What is... what is
happening to me...?
Yeah... That was going
to be my next question.
Uh...
Miss Stella...
what are you doing?
(embarrassed squeal)
(loud thud)
Owww!
Ikki:
Okay. There ya go.
Uh... thank you...
I'm just glad it
wasn't a concussion.
Stella:
I'm sorry.
Hmm?
I despised everyone
at home because
they put this
label on me...
And then I did the same
exact thing to you.
I couldn't see you
for what you were.
If I'd tried harder,
I wouldn't have
freaked out like that...
Well, I'm done
freaking out... Ikki!
Okay.
(box closes)
So now you're...
...you're gonna be,
like, my servant, right?
Huh?
"The loser will obey
the winner for the rest
of her life," remember?
"The loser will obey
the winner for the rest
of her life," remember?
Oh!
No wait I didn't think
we were taking that seriously!
The deal was‐ you do
what I say, right...?
No wait I didn't think
we were taking that seriously!
The deal was‐ you do
what I say, right...?
Ikki:
"Anything..."?
Mmm...
Wait‐ anything?! There's no way
buddy! The deal is off!
'Kay... so the Royal Vermillion
family is not so great
at honoring treaties,
then, I guess...?
(offended exhale)
HOW DARE YOU SAY SUCH A THING!
FINE! Then I'll be
your servant, or your dog,
or whatever you want!
Make me bend
to your evil wishes!
Use me for your
villainous sexual desires!
Pervert! Peasant!
I... hate you! Hmph!
(laughs)
Stella:
What's so funny?!
Okay then this is
your order... Miss Stella...
I order you to be my roommate.
Huh?
Miss Stella... I want us
to be closer‐ to be friends...
Um...! "Closer..." What...?
I am a Princess!
That is... just so
inappropriate...
Well then I guess if
we can't be roommates...
Ikki:
Then we should probably...
go talk to the Director...
No... no I...
don't...
Huh? "Don't" what?
Let me be clear!
I made a deal.
I will honor it‐ but I have
no desire to be "closer" to you!
Stella:
Do you understand?
Heh. That's fair enough...
Miss Stella.
(softens tone)
Stella.
Huh?
It's just "Stella."
Or the agreement is off!
(moved sigh)
Okay... that's cool... "Stella."
Well alright then.
Uh?
Heh.
(fist bump)