-LONG AGO, THERE WAS A WARRIOR.
IN ORDER TO PROTECT HIS FRIEND,
THE WARRIOR HAD TO TAKE
HIS FRIEND'S LIFE.
LONG AGO, THERE WAS A SWORD.
THIS SWORD HAD CONTINUED
TO FIGHT FOR PEACE,
YET REALIZED
THAT TO PROTECT THE PEACE,
IT HAD NO CHOICE BUT TO KILL
THE ONE WHO WIELDED IT,
AND THUS
TOOK ITS MASTER'S LIFE.
THE WARRIOR AND THE SWORD
HAD TO DO WHAT THEY DID,
BUT WAS THAT REALLY WHAT
THEY OUGHT TO HAVE DONE?
UNCERTAIN OF THE ANSWER
EVEN NOW,
THEY WANDER AIMLESSLY.
[ RITSUKO OKAZAKI'S
"MORNING GRACE" PLAYING ]
-♪ YONDE IRU KOE ♪
♪ SAA ME O SAMASHITE ♪
♪ NAKIGAO NUGUTTE ♪
♪ MABUSHII HIKARI ♪
♪ KIGI NO TSUYU ♪
♪ UMARERU ♪
♪ DARE MO SHIRANAI ♪
♪ HIMITSU NO MIZUBE DE ♪
♪ ODORE INOCHI NO PA DO DU ♪
♪ KYOU MO YUME MITERU ♪
♪ SORE WA YASASHIKU ♪
♪ HAGESHII NAGARE NE ♪
♪ DOKO MADE TSUZUKU RABIRINSU ♪
♪ WATASHI WA YUKOU ♪
♪ NIGIRISHIMERU YUME ♪
[ TCHAIKOVSKY'S
"WALTZ OF THE FLOWERS" PLAYING ]
[ BIRDS CHIRPING ]
-[ Thinking ]
WHERE ARE YOU, MYTHO?
THERE'S NOWHERE ELSE LEFT
FOR ME TO LOOK.
[ THUD ]
-HMM?
-HER AGAIN.
[ THUD ]
-HMM. PERSISTENT GIRL.
-FAKIR?
-SO YOU'RE AWAKE.
-WHERE'S TUTU?
-DON'T WORRY.
TUTU IS LONG GONE.
WHAT HAPPENED?
-TUTU HELPED ME.
-HMM?
-SHE TRIED TO RESTORE
PART OF MY HEART TO ME.
-MYTHO, YOU KNOW --
-THAT'S WHEN KRAEHE CAME.
-KRAEHE?
-YES.
SHE WAS DRESSED LIKE
A BLACK BIRD
AND SHE TOOK THE PIECE.
TELL ME, FAKIR, WOULDN'T IT...
WOULDN'T IT BE BETTER FOR ME
IF I REGAINED ALL THE PIECES
OF MY HEART?
-FORGET ABOUT IT.
-BUT...
-LISTEN TO ME,
I BROUGHT YOU BACK HERE
BECAUSE I THOUGHT IT WOULD BE
SAFER TO HAVE PEOPLE AROUND.
BURY YOUR WORRIES IN SLEEP.
[ SIGHS ]
[ BIRDS CHIRPING ]
[ MOANS ]
-WHAT...WHAT IS THIS?
[ GASPS ]
-WHY?
-WHO'S THERE?
-WHY DID YOU BRING ME
BACK WITH YOU?
-ARE YOU MYTHO'S...
I-I BROUGHT YOU WITH ME?
WHAT DO YOU MEAN?
-[ CHUCKLES ]
YOU WANT TO KNOW A LOT,
DON'T YOU?
I KNOW HOW YOU FEEL
BECAUSE I HAVE THE DESIRE
FOR KNOWLEDGE.
-DESIRE FOR KNOWLEDGE?
-YOU DON'T REMEMBER
HOW YOU BROUGHT ME HERE?
-I-I BROUGHT YOU?
YOU'RE LYING.
-WHY DO YOU DON BLACK FEATHERS?
-[ GASPS ]
NO!
-DO YOU HAVE A SPECIAL POWER
DWELLING WITHIN YOU?
COME ON, TELL ME.
WHICH ONE IS THE REAL YOU?
-STOP IT.
-WHO ARE YOU, REALLY?
-STOP!
[ OPENS DRAWER ]
[ BOX THUDS ]
[ SLAMS DRAWER ]
[ BREATHES HEAVILY ]
-I SAW YOU!
-HUH?
-I SAW YOU FOR SURE!
[ Muffled screaming ]
-CONFESSING YOUR LOVE
AT THE WINDOW?
DUCK, YOU'RE SO BOLD!
-WHAT?
-IT WAS LIKE A REVERSE
ROMEO AND JULIET,
BUT HORRIBLY DIFFERENT
IN THAT IT WAS SO ONE-SIDED.
-NO, THAT'S NOT IT.
MYTHO DISAPPEARED, AND I --
-RIGHT! I FORGOT!
HE HASN'T BEEN TO CLASS
IN A LONG TIME, HUH?
-THAT'S WHY YOU COULDN'T
CONTAIN YOURSELF
AND RESOLVED TO CONFESS.
-NO, IT ISN'T!
-TAKE THIS CHANCE
TO ATTACK, ATTACK, ATTACK!
-THOUGH YOU REALLY HAVE NO HELP
SINCE THE WONDERFUL MYTHO
ALREADY HAS RUE.
-GO FOR IT! TAKE YOUR LOSSES.
-LOSE AND BE CRUSHED!
-BUT -- BUT I WAS JUST --
-HE MIGHT SHOW UP
FOR CLASS TODAY!
-WHAT? YOU THINK SO?
-YOU'RE HOPEFUL, AREN'T YOU?
THAT'S SO CUTE!
[ INDISTINCT CONVERSATIONS ]
-WILL MYTHO COME TODAY?
-IF HE DOES, YOU HAVE TO SAY IT
LOUD AND CLEAR!
-HUH? SAY WHAT?
-OH, COME ON, DUCK. WHAT ELSE?
-HUH?
-THAT YOU LOVE HIM!
-WHAT?!
I CAN'T TELL HIM THAT BECAUSE...
[ Thinking ] BECAUSE IF I SAID
THAT, I'D VANISH.
-OH, YOU COULD!
-[ SCREAMS ]
-WAIT, WHERE'S SHE GOING?
-IT WAS YOUR FAULT!
-NO WAY!
-[ GASP ]
-[ SQUEALS ]
-[ GROANS ]
-DUCK?
-HUH?
-WHAT ARE YOU DOING?
-[ GASPS ] MYTHO!
-YOU'RE ALL RIGHT.
I'M SO GLAD!
-[ SCREAMING ]
-[ SCREAMS ]
I'M SORRY, I'M SO SORRY!
I LOOKED ALL OVER TOWN
BUT I COULDN'T FIND YOU
SO I WAS WONDERING
WHAT HAPPENED TO YOU.
AND NOW SEEING YOU'RE OKAY,
IT'S SUCH A RELIEF AND I-I --
[ LAUGHS NERVOUSLY ]
I'M JUST GLAD THAT YOU'RE OKAY.
-YOU WERE LOOKING FOR ME?
-[ Thinking ] OH! THAT'S RIGHT.
HE DOESN'T KNOW I'M TUTU, SO...
-HUH? TUTU?
-UH...
-DO YOU KNOW ABOUT TUTU, DUCK?
-UH, UM, WELL...
-WHAT ARE YOU DOING?
-FAKIR!
-MYTHO, YOU GO AHEAD.
I'LL BE RIGHT THERE.
-YES.
-[ Whimpers ]
-NOW YOU...
-[ GASPS ] YES?
[ Whimpers ]
-YOU'RE SUCH AN EYESORE.
LISTEN CAREFULLY --
NEVER COME NEAR MYTHO AGAIN.
IF YOU DO, I'LL MAKE SURE
YOU PAY FOR IT.
[ Whimpers ]
[ Whimpering ]
-SO, WHAT WAS THE OUTCOME?
DOES THIS MEAN SHE FAILED?
-IT WAS A RATHER SUBDUED
LETDOWN.
BUT WE'LL SET A REVENGE MATCH
FOR HER.
-[ Thinking ] LAST NIGHT,
I SAW TUTU RETURN A PIECE
OF MYTHO'S HEART TO HIM.
MYTHO ALSO WISHED
FOR ITS RETURN.
THEN...I SAW THAT,
AND AFTER THAT,
WHAT...
WHO -- WHO AM I?
[ BELL TOLLS ]
-[ SIGHS ]
[ Thinking ] I SKIPPED
ALL MY MORNING CLASSES.
[ SIGHS ]
FAKIR HAD THAT SCARY LOOK
IN HIS EYES.
MYTHO SHOULDN'T BE WITH
SOMEONE LIKE THAT.
BUT WHAT SHOULD I DO?
[ MUSIC PLAYING ]
-OH, HELLO, MISS EDEL.
-YES, HELLO, DUCK.
-MISS EDEL, I NEED SOME HELP.
I WANNA SAVE MYTHO FROM FAKIR,
BUT FAKIR TOLD ME NOT
TO GO NEAR MYTHO
OR ELSE HE'D MAKE ME PAY FOR IT.
WHICH KIND OF SCARES ME,
BUT, I MEAN, I RATHER...
HUH?
-THE NAME OF THIS GEM
IS "COURAGE,"
A SINGLE GEM MADE OF TWO.
-[ Thinking ]
DOES THAT MEAN I SHOULD
WORK TOGETHER WITH SOMEONE?
BUT WHO?
I CAN'T PUT RUE IN DANGER.
[ GASPS ]
-I WANT YOU
TO RESTORE MY HEART, TUTU.
-[ Thinking ] IF -- IF I LET
MYTHO KNOW THAT I'M TUTU,
THEN TOGETHER, WE MIGHT BE ABLE
TO STAND UP TO FAKIR.
-FAKIR?
WHAT IS FAKIR TO YOU, DUCK?
-HUH? WHAT IS HE?
NOTHING REALLY TO ME,
BUT HE'S A DANGEROUS PERSON
TO MYTHO.
OH!
WHAT?
MISS EDEL!
[ BIRDS CHIRPING ]
-QUACK! QUACK, QUACK, QUACK.
-[ Thinking ] ALL RIGHT.
[ SNIFFING ]
THIS IS IT!
NO DOUBT ABOUT IT.
IT'S MYTHO'S SMELL!
QUACK, QUACK, QUACK, QUACK!
[ DOOR CREAKS ]
[ GASPS ]
[ Thinking ]
OH, NO! SOMEONE'S COMING!
QUACK, QUACK!
[ DOOR CLOSES ]
- [ Thinking ] AN IGUANA?
[ SIGHS ]
THAT WAS CLOSE.
[ DOOR OPENS ]
-QUACK! [ GROANING ]
[ Thinking ] WH -- WHAT? WHAT?!
-THERE.
YOU'RE SO STUPID.
THERE'S NO WAY YOU WERE
GOING TO FIND ANY FOOD IN THERE.
[ CHUCKLES ]
I GUESS YOU WOULDN'T HAVE
WANDERED IN IF YOU KNEW.
-QUA -- QUACK, QUACK, QUACK,
QUACK, QUACK.
-[ LAUGHS ]
YOU SURE EAT A LOT.
HURRY HOME.
DON'T COME AROUND ANYMORE.
-[ Thinking ] SOMEHOW,
HE WASN'T LIKE THE USUAL FAKIR.
-IF YOU DO, I'LL MAKE SURE
YOU PAY FOR IT.
-[ Thinking ]
NO, NO, NO, NO, NO, NO, NO!
HE'S DEFINITELY A BAD GUY.
I'M NOT GONNA BE FOOLED JUST
BECAUSE THE BREAD WAS TASTY.
HE PROBABLY ACTED LIKE THAT
ONLY BECAUSE I WAS JUST A DUCK.
A DUCK?
IF I'M GONNA TELL MYTHO
EVERYTHING,
I BETTER TELL HIM
THAT I'M JUST A DUCK, TOO,
SHOULDN'T I?
QUACK, QUACK, QUACK.
[ TCHAIKOVSKY'S "DANCE OF
THE SUGAR PLUM FAIRY" PLAYING ]
[ INDISTINCT CONVERSATIONS ]
-WHAT'S THAT?
-DUCK SAYS SHE HAS SOMETHING
IMPORTANT TO TELL ME.
-"I'LL BE WAITING
IN THE SCHOOL'S BACKYARD
AT 5:00 THIS EVENING. DUCK."
-DID THAT GIRL NOT HEAR
WHAT I SAID TO HER?
[ SCOFFS ] THROW IT AWAY.
THERE'S NO NEED TO GO.
-NO.
-WHAT?
-I'VE CHOSEN TO GO, FAKIR.
-YOU'RE KIDDING, RIGHT?
-I MEAN IT.
-WHAT POINT IS THERE?
-MAYBE THERE'S SOMETHING
SHE CAN TELL ME ABOUT TUTU.
-WHO? DUCK?
-YES.
-MORON.
THERE'S NO WAY SHE COULD KNOW.
-BUT --
-DON'T GET INVOLVED WITH TUTU.
HER EXISTENCE WILL JUST BRING
YOU UNHAPPINESS IN THE END.
DON'T BE FOOLED.
-HUH?
-AND ON TOP OF THAT,
YOU HAVE THAT KRAEHE
CHASING AFTER YOU RIGHT NOW.
-I DON'T CARE.
-IF I TELL YOU, "NO," IT'S NO!
YOU GOT THAT?
-NO.
[ SLAPS ]
-THAT'S ENOUGH FROM YOU!
-OH, MY GOSH.
-HE SLAPPED HIM.
-I'M SORRY.
-I AM GOING.
-[ GROANS ]
SO I'M NO LONGER ABLE
TO STOP MYTHO WITH WORDS.
[ RUNNING FOOTSTEPS ]
-[ PANTING ]
[ FOOTSTEPS DESCENDING ]
-UH-OH.
THAT IS THE PRINCE'S OWN SWORD,
WHICH ONCE SHATTERED HIS HEART.
NOW WHAT DO YOU PLAN
TO DO WITH IT?
[ LAUGHS EVILLY ]
-[ SPEAKING GERMAN ]
[ SWORD ZINGS ]
[ SWORD SLASHES ]
[ SHATTERS ]
-MYTHO.
[ INHALES DEEPLY,
EXHALES SLOWLY ]
[ FOOTSTEPS APPROACH ]
-OH.
[ GASPS ]
I-E-I-E-I...O.
-HUH?
-IS THAT DUCK?
-UM, I-I, UH, ACTUALLY,
ACTUALLY...
DO, DO, DO, DO.
-TUTU.
-HUH? NO WAY.
YOU KNEW ALL ALONG?
-YOU KNOW ABOUT TUTU,
DON'T YOU, DUCK?
-HUH? OHH. YOU SCARED ME.
-FAKIR TOLD ME THAT
I SHOULDN'T COME HERE, BUT...
-YOU TOLD FAKIR ABOUT THIS?
-YES.
-[ GROANS ]
[ Thinking ] RIGHT.
EVERYTHING I TELL MYTHO
GOES STRAIGHT TO FAKIR, TOO.
-DUCK.
-YES?
-I-I WANT TO SEE TUTU.
-HUH?
-WHENEVER I THINK OF TUTU,
I BECOME FILLED WITH
THE DESIRE TO SEE HER.
-MYTHO...
-I WANT TO BE WITH TUTU ALWAYS.
[ WINGS FLUTTER ]
-[ GASPS ]
[ SCREAMS, GROANS ]
-MY PRINCE, YOU BELONG TO ME.
-KRAEHE?
-[ LAUGHS ] THAT'S RIGHT!
THAT'S THE SPIRIT!
THE VALUE OF TREASURE IS
REVEALED WHEN IT'S FOUGHT OVER.
NOW, WHICH DESERVING MAID
WILL THE PRINCE WANT TO GO TO,
MY DEAR PRINCESS TUTU?
[ BUBBLING ]
[ TINKLING ]
[ DING ]
-YOUR HAIR, YOUR CHEEKS,
EVEN YOUR HEART.
EVERYTHING BELONGS TO ME.
-PLEASE, STOP.
KRAEHE.
-PRINCESS TUTU.
-RETURN THE HEART SHARD
YOU TOOK.
STOP MAKING THE PRINCE SUFFER.
-TUTU...
-I'M TREMBLING.
LOOK, MY PRINCE,
THERE'S THE ONE MAKING YOU
SUFFER -- PRINCESS TUTU.
-WHAT?
-NO!
NO, THAT'S A LIE!
-MY POOR PRINCE,
I'M THE ONE YOU NEED.
I ALONE.
I WILL ALWAYS BE WITH YOU.
-KRAEHE.
-YOU'RE LIKE A DOLL,
BUT I WILL LOVE YOU.
I WILL MAKE YOU FORGET TUTU.
WE'LL JUST GIVE THESE
HEART THINGS TO THE CROWS.
-[ GASPS ] NO!
[ RAVENS CAWING ]
[ WIND GUSTS ]
[ SWORD ZINGS ]
-THAT'S THE PRINCE'S SWORD.
-SO, YOU'RE KRAEHE?
-HOW DARE YOU ADDRESS ME, FILTH!
-ARE YOU THE RAVEN'S MANIFEST?
[ GROANS ]
[ FABRIC RIPS,
OBJECT CLATTERS ]
[ WINGS FLUTTER ]
-WHO AM I SUPPOSED TO BE?
[ SHATTERS ]
-THE SHARD!
-IT'S NO USE...
PRINCESS TUTU.
-WHO ARE...
[ ARMOR CLATTERS ]
-FAKIR!
-SORRY YOU'VE HAD TO WAIT,
MYTHO.
IT'S ALL RIGHT NOW.
YOU WON'T HAVE TO SUFFER.
-WHAT ARE YOU DOING?
-SIT DOWN.
I'LL SET THINGS RIGHT.
I WILL SHATTER YOUR HEART
FOR YOU ONCE AGAIN.
-WHAT?!
-AND YOU WILL NOT STOP ME,
PRINCESS TUTU!
-MYTHO!
YOU, FAKIR? YOU'RE THE ONE
WHO SHATTERED MYTHO'S HEART?
WHY'D YOU DO
SUCH AN AWFUL THING?
[ TCHAIKOVSKY'S
"FANTASY OVERTURE" PLAYING ]
-IF YOU HAD NOT SHOWN UP,
THEN NONE OF THIS
WOULD'VE HAPPENED.
-I...
-TUTU...
-[ GROANS ]
-[ GASPS ]
-FAKIR, STOP IT!
-PRINCE!
[ SWORD CLATTERS ]
-[ GASPS ]
-IS IT MY FAULT?
IF I PIERCED MY HEART
WITH THIS SWORD,
WILL THAT SATISFY YOU, FAKIR?
-THAT'S RIGHT. THEN YOU'LL
RETURN TO YOUR OLD SELF.
-ALL RIGHT.
-WHAT?
[ SWORD CLANGS ]
-[ GASPS ] MYTHO!
DON'T DO IT!
MYTHO!
YOU'D RATHER BE
WITHOUT A HEART?!
-DO IT! QUICKLY!
PIECE YOUR HEART!
-MYTHO, PLEASE, DON'T!
NO! NO!
-DO IT NOW.
DO IT!
-NO!
THE OTHER DAY YOU SMILED,
REMEMBER?
WHEN I SAW THAT, I THOUGHT,
THIS MUST BE THE REAL YOU.
I BELIEVE IF YOUR HEART
IS FULLY RESTORED
THEN YOU'D BE ABLE TO SHOW
EVEN MORE OF YOURSELF
BECAUSE THAT'S THE REAL YOU!
[ CRYING ]
I'M SORRY.
[ TINKLES ]
[ CRYING ]
I CAN'T SAVE OR PROTECT YOU
FROM THE SUFFERING.
BECAUSE ALL I CAN DO
IS RESTORE YOUR HEART TO YOU.
THAT'S IT.
[ CRYING ]
[ SWORD CLANGS ]
-MYTHO.
-I SEE.
SO THIS IS THE ANSWER
YOU HAVE CHOSEN.
-TUTU, RESTORE THIS HEART SHARD
TO ME.
[ GASPS ]
AAH!
OH.
PRINCESS TUTU.
I WANT TO KNOW...
-HUH?
-WHAT DO YOU THINK OF ME?
I WANT TO KNOW.
-I...
UH, I...
-WAIT. TUTU.
WHY ARE YOU RUNNING, TUTU?
-[ Thinking ] I'M A DUCK.
I'M REALLY ONLY A BIRD.
BUT WHAT THE PRINCE SEES
IS PRINCESS TUTU
IN HER BEAUTIFUL DRESS.
IT'S NOT ME.
[ BELL TOLLING ]
-WAS WHAT THE SWORD PIERCED
THE PRINCE'S HEART?
OR WAS IT SOMEONE'S FEELINGS?
[ LAUGHS EVILLY ]
[ RITSUKO OKAZAKI'S "ALTHOUGH
MY LOVE IS SMALL" PLAYING ]
-♪ YUME MIRU ♪
♪ YOU NI ♪
♪ KOI O SHITA NO ♪
♪ FUKURAMU ♪
♪ KOKORO GA FUKURAMU NO YO ♪
♪ IKITERUTTE SUTEKI
NA KOTO TO OMOTTA ♪
♪ ASU GA MACHI DOOSHII ♪
♪ MM ♪
♪ ANATA NO CHIKARA NI NARITAI
NO DONNA TOKI NI MO WATASHI ♪
♪ MATTE MATTE
KURENAI HASHITTE ♪
♪ HASHITTE IKU NO YO ♪
♪ KAZE MO AMAGUMO
MO OIKOSHITE ♪
♪ WATASHI DAKE
NO TSUBASA HABATAITE ♪
-I AM RUE.
I'M NOT ANYONE ELSE.
THAT'S WHO I'VE ALWAYS BEEN.
-RUE, MAYBE I'M ACTUALLY...
-ONCE AGAIN,
PRINCESS TUTU WILL CHANGE MYTHO.
-KRAEHE,
WHY ARE YOU IN SUCH PAIN?
-BEGONE, YOU UGLY CROW.
-THAT'S RIGHT. I AM A CROW.
AND I, ALONE,
AM THE TRUE PRIMA DONNA,
PRINCESS KRAEHE.
-ALL WHO LOVE STORIES,
GATHER 'ROUND.
[ LAUGHS EVILLY ]