-ONCE UPON A TIME,
THERE WAS A YOUNG MAN
WITH A BEAUTIFUL FACE.
THE PEOPLE LOVED
THE HANDSOME YOUNG MAN,
BUT HE NEVER SHOWED
THE SLIGHTEST INTEREST
IN LOVING ANYONE.
THIS WAS BECAUSE ALL HE LOVED
WAS HIMSELF.
WHEN THE YOUNG MAN
WHO NEGLECTED TO LOVE
AND SOUGHT ONLY TO BE LOVED
FOUND SOMEONE
FOR WHOM HE TRULY CARED,
HE REALIZED THAT HE HAD LOST
EVEN THE WORDS
TO EXPRESS THOSE FEELINGS.
[ RITSUKO OKAZAKI'S
"MORNING GRACE" PLAYS ]
-[ SINGING IN JAPANESE ]
[ SINGING CONTINUES ]
[ TCHAIKOVSKY'S
"FINAL WALTZ AND APOTHEOSIS"
FROM "THE NUTCRACKER" PLAYS ]
-[ GROANS ]
[ WIND HOWLS ]
-CALM DOWN, FATHER.
IF YOU GET EXCITED,
IT WILL AFFECT YOUR HEALTH.
-YOU STILL DON'T HAVE THE HEART,
THE YOUNG AND BEAUTIFUL HEART
FOR ME.
-YOU SEE, PRINCESS TUTU
INTERFERES EVERY TIME.
-DON'T GIVE ME EXCUSES.
-BUT, FATHER!
WHEN HE SEES PRINCESS TUTU,
THE OLD PRINCE
STARTS TO AWAKEN AGAIN.
SO, I --
-IF YOU'RE A GIRL
OF NOBLE RAVEN BIRTH,
CEASE THIS INCESSANT WHINING.
HURRY AND FETCH ME A HEART!
-I UNDERSTAND.
PLEASE, CALM YOURSELF, FATHER.
-[ GROWLS ]
-POOR FATHER.
-OH, THE WONDERFUL MYTHO.
WHEN I THINK ABOUT MYTHO,
I'M OVERCOME WITH FEELING
EVEN WHILE I'M EATING LIKE THIS.
-ALL OF MY THOUGHTS
IMMEDIATELY TURN TO MYTHO.
-HM?
-HUH?
[ WIND RUSTLING ]
-OH, NO.
WE'D BETTER HURRY AND GET
TO OUR CLASSROOM ON THE DOUBLE.
-HEY, YOU'RE RIGHT.
-LET'S HURRY!
-YOU DON'T CARE ANYMORE
ABOUT MYTHO, EITHER,
RIGHT, DUCK?
-HUH?
-HEY, I GET YOU.
HE'S KIND OF CHANGED, HASN'T HE?
-H-HE HAS?
-THE MYSTERIOUS SIDE IS GONE.
OR, RATHER, DON'T YOU FEEL LIKE
HE'LL TAKE ANY GIRL?
-HE'S A BEAST.
-YOU TWO.
-BUT, YOU KNOW,
TEEN HEARTTHROBS NEED TO BE
A LITTLE MORE APPROACHABLE,
ANYWAY.
-YOU MEAN THEY SHOULD BE
MILDLY STUPID?
-IT'S BECAUSE HE'S NOT
THE REAL MYTHO.
-AFTER ALL, YOU RETURNED
THE FEELING OF LOVE
TO THE PRINCE,
IGNORANT OF THE FACT
THAT IT WAS DYED
IN THE RAVEN'S BLOOD.
-TUTU, HELP ME.
-MYTHO'S GOT TO BE THE ONE
WHO'S SUFFERING THE MOST.
I WANT TO RETURN HIM TO
THE OLD MYTHO AS SOON AS I CAN.
BUT HOW DO I DO THAT?
-BONJOUR.
-UH...
-MADEMOISELLE.
-MAD--
-[ MOOS ]
[ FANFARE PLAYS ]
-UH, PIKE, LILIE?
AAH!
-OH, YOUNG LADY
WHO HAS EYES OF TRUTH,
PLEASE, TAKE THIS.
-[ LAUGHS ]
UM, OKAY.
THANK YOU VERY MUCH?
-THOUGH THIS TRIFLE COULD
NEVER HOPE TO HOLD A CANDLE
TO THE GREATNESS OF YOUR LOVE.
[ LAUGHS ]
-UM...WHO ARE YOU?
-NO. NO.
-OH.
I UNDERSTAND YOUR DESIRE
TO KNOW EVERYTHING ABOUT ME,
BUT IT'S ONE I MUSTN'T FULFILL
BECAUSE...
I AM QUALIFIED TO BE
A TRUE PRINCE,
ONE WHO LOVES EVERYONE...
AND IS ALSO LOVED BY EVERYONE.
-WHAT?
A...TRUE PRINCE?
-HOWEVER, RIGHT NOW,
THE LADIES OF THIS ACADEMY
ARE CONSIGNING THEMSELVES
TO THAT MAN'S FALSE LOVE!
[ SOBS ]
-YOU MEAN MYTHO?
-THAT MUST BE BECAUSE...
[Weakly] OF MY OWN SHORTCOMINGS,
MUSTN'T IT?
[ Voice breaking ] BECAUSE
I CAN'T GIVE AWAY ENOUGH LOVE.
OH, HEAVEN!
POUR JUDGMENT UPON THIS SINNER!
HERE! OLé!
-OLé!
-QUACK!
-[ MOOS ]
-[ WHIMPERS ]
-[ CHUCKLES ]
SO FLUSTERED.
I SEE MON CHéRIE IS A SHY ONE.
ALAS,
THIS ALL-TOO-LENIENT PUNISHMENT
CANNOT COMPARE TO THE PAIN
IN THE HEARTS OF THE WOMEN
WHOM I AM HURTING.
-MASTER FEMIO.
-QUACK.
QUACK.
[ SIGHS ]
MAN, THAT SCARED ME.
"TRUE PRINCE" --
WAS THAT GUY JUST NOW
A PRINCE, TOO?
-WHAT ARE YOU PLAYING AT?
-HUH?
-WHAT DO YOU MEAN?
-IT WOULD BE CRUEL
TO POOR FATHER
IF WE DIDN'T GET HIM
A SACRIFICIAL HEART TO EAT SOON.
-YES.
-HE'S NEVER BEEN VERY PATIENT,
YOU KNOW?
-[ GASPS ]
-I'M SICK OF WAITING, AS WELL.
IS SOMEONE THERE?
-TUT--
HI, DUCK.
YOU CAN GO, MYTHO.
-I SHOULD --
-GO ON.
GET GOING.
-ALL RIGHT.
-[ GASPS ] MYTHO!
WAIT!
-FORGET IT.
-BUT, RUE, I --
-I'VE ALREADY TOLD YOU
THERE IS NO RUE.
-THAT'S NOT TRUE.
I DON'T BELIEVE THAT.
I GET THIS FEELING
YOU'RE STILL RUE.
-[ CHUCKLES ]
IT HONESTLY DOESN'T MATTER
WHAT IT IS YOU THINK.
IT'S DONE NOW,
AND THE PRINCE IS MINE.
-PRINCE?
DID YOU CALL ME?
[ FANFARE PLAYS ]
-HM?
-YOUNG LADY.
-OOH!
QUA--
[ GRUNTS ]
[ MUFFLED SCREAM ]
-GIVE ME YOUR HAND,
S'IL VOUS PLAîT.
[ CHUCKLES ] YOU DON'T HAVE TO
BE SO SHY, MY CUTE ONE.
[ BIZET'S "HABANERA" PLAYS ]
YOU BLOOM LIKE A FLOWER.
YOU FLY AWAY LIKE A SONGBIRD.
OH, LOVELY YOU.
[ FOOTSTEPS ]
OH?
THAT YOUNG LADY
IS TRULY A TIMID SOUL.
-MM-HMM.
-[ GRUNTS ]
THIS CURSED BODY.
EVEN AS THEY ARE DRAWN
TO ITS BEAUTY,
ITS PERFECTION
HALTS THEIR APPROACH.
[ GASPS ]
AN INTENSE GAZE?
MADEMOISELLE, I BEG YOUR PARDON
FOR ONLY JUST NOW NOTICING
YOUR FERVENT GAZE.
-YOU SAY YOU'RE A PRINCE, HUH?
-CORRECT.
I AM QUALIFIED
TO BE A TRUE PRINCE,
ONE WHO LOVES EVERYONE
AND IS ALSO LOVED BY EVERYONE.
ONE DAY, I'LL BE
A GREAT ENOUGH MAN
TO ACCEPT ALL THE WORLD'S LOVE,
I PROMISE YOU.
WHEN THAT HAPPENS,
I'M SURE NO ONE WILL BE
ABLE TO HELP BUT LOVE ME.
-ONLY MYSELF.
NO ONE BUT THE PRINCE
IN THE STORY
CAN TRULY LOVE
A PITIFUL PERSON LIKE YOU
WHO, DESPITE BEING A CROW,
HAS BEEN BORN
INTO THIS HIDEOUS HUMAN BODY.
-WHAT SPLENDID CONFIDENCE.
WHAT BLINDING PRIDE --
ENOUGH TO MAKE ME HATE YOU.
YOU'RE QUITE WONDERFUL.
-MASTER FEMIO, BY ANY CHANCE,
COULD THIS POSSIBLY BE...
-BE WHAT?
-...THE TIME FOR YOU TO MAKE
A GRAND DISPLAY
OF YOUR ATTRACTIVENESS,
MASTER FEMIO?
-AH!
-NOW, THEN, TODAY, WE WILL BE
TESTING YOUR ABILITIES.
THERE IS, HOWEVER,
NO NEED TO BE NERVOUS.
IF YOU HAVE NOT NEGLECTED
YOUR EVERYDAY PRACTICING,
YOU SHOULD HAVE NO PROBLEM.
-AT TIMES LIKE THIS,
IT SEEMS LIKE NOTHING'S CHANGED
BUT...MYTHO.
-FIRST UP WILL BE MR. MYT--
-MR. CAT.
PARDON ME, BUT I BELIEVE
I'M THE APPROPRIATE CHOICE
TO DANCE THE FIRST SOLO.
-[ YOWLS ]
MR. FEMIO, YOU'RE ON PROBATION!
-CONTACT WITH TRUE ART
IS A VALUABLE AND ENRICHING
EXPERIENCE FOR EVERYONE.
-HUH?
-HE'S GOT GUTS
FOR SOMEONE ON PROBATION.
-MAYBE HE'S REALLY GOOD
OR SOMETHING.
-MAYBE HE'S JUST...WEIRD.
[ STUDENTS MURMURING ]
-UH, MR. FEMIO, IT'S NOT THAT
I DON'T UNDERSTAND
YOUR QUEST FOR ART,
BUT LEARNING AND MASTERING
THE BASICS FIRST --
-IT'S QUITE ALL RIGHT.
IT IS A CURSE OF GENIUS TO BE
MISUNDERSTOOD IN EVERY ERA.
BUT, SOMEDAY, THIS DANCE OF
MINE, THIS VERY LOVE OF MINE,
WILL SATISFY THE HEARTS
OF ALL PEOPLE.
YES, 'TIS DESTINY.
YOU KNOW, MR. CAT,
IF I WERE A WOMAN,
I WOULD HAVE TAKEN
YOUR HAND IN MARRIAGE!
-[ YOWLS QUIETLY ]
-HOWEVER, I'M NOT.
-[ YOWLING ]
-MONTAND.
MY GODDESS.
-HUH?
-THIS FEELING NEEDS NO WORDS
TO EXPRESS IT.
-A FEELING EXPRESSED
WITHOUT EVEN...A WORD.
-WHAT'S WRONG?
-AND ONE FOR YOU
WITH THE INTENT GAZE.
[ GASPS ]
-[ GASPS ] MYTHO.
THAT'S THE MIME
FOR "I LOVE YOU."
-[ GROANS ]
[ STUDENTS GASP, MURMUR ]
-IS HE OKAY?
-M-MYTHO!
-WORDS WITHOUT A VOICE.
ARE THEY A SIGN OF THE PRINCE'S
RETURN TO HIS OLD SELF...
OR RATHER A PITIFUL DEATH CRY?
[ LAUGHS EVILLY ]
WHICH SHALL IT BE?
WHICH ONE SHALL IT BE?
[ TCHAIKOVSKY'S "MARCH"
FROM "THE NUTCRACKER" PLAYS ]
-OHH, I CAN'T BELIEVE IT!
-WHAT A SHOCK.
-THAT WAS DEFINITELY THE
"I LOVE YOU" MIME, WASN'T IT?
-RIGHT AT FEMIO.
-COME TO THINK OF IT, FEMIO GAVE
DUCK A FLOWER, TOO, DIDN'T HE?
-YEAH, HE AND DUCK
WOULD GO WELL TOGETHER.
-WHAT'S THAT MEAN, ZURA?
-HM? "GO WELL TOGETHER"?
-MAYBE IT MEANS "LOVEY-DOVEY."
-DUCK IS LOVEY-DOVEY, ZURA?
-WE'RE SAYING THAT
WOULD HAVE BEEN BETTER.
-OH! THANKS, ZURA.
[ DRUM BEATS ]
-AND HERE, I THOUGHT THAT
FINALLY DUCK'S PRINCE HAD COME.
-THINGS SURE HAVE GOTTEN
COMPLICATED.
-THEY SURE HAVE.
WHO WOULD HAVE THOUGHT
THAT SHE AND THE OLD PRINCE
WOULD ACTUALLY BECOME RIVALS
FOR THE NEW PRINCE'S LOVE?
-HE'S A PRINCE, TOO?
-OF COURSE NOT, SILLY.
-HE'S JUST CLAIMING HE'S ONE.
-HMM.
-HEY, WHY DON'T YOU TAKE
THIS CHANCE TO DATE FEMIO?
-THAT WOULD BE GREAT.
-HUH?
-THOUGH THIS PRINCE
IS WAY BELOW THE LAST ONE.
-I SEE IT NOW --
HE AND DUCK WON'T GET ALONG,
AND THEY'LL NEVER BE ON THE SAME
PAGE, SO IT'S SURE TO BE FUN.
-FUN?
-ABSOLUTELY --
SO FUN I COULD WATCH ALL DAY
AND NEVER GET BORED.
-BUT, STILL, I GOT TO SAY
IT'S NOT TOTALLY CLEAR
WHETHER THE WONDERFUL MYTHO'S
DESPERATE MIME OF LOVE
WAS REALLY MEANT
FOR FEMIO OR NOT.
-OH?
THEN WHO WAS IT FOR?
-I DON'T KNOW, ALL THE GIRLS?
-WHAT A BEAST!
-MYTHO.
I THINK THAT WAS THE REAL MYTHO
BECAUSE HE SEEMED SO -- SO SAD.
HIS EYES SHOWED SO MUCH PAIN.
-IT LOOKS LIKE YOU'RE FEELING
QUITE A BIT BETTER.
-YES.
SORRY FOR MAKING YOU WORRY.
-DID SOMETHING HAPPEN?
-[ GRUNTS ]
-THAT MIME WAS, INDEED,
QUITE SPLENDID,
BUT IT SEEMED SO SORROWFUL
AND FRAGILE
THAT I MUST SAY
I'M A BIT CONCERNED.
-NOTHING HAPPENED.
-I SEE.
WELL, REST
FOR A LITTLE WHILE LONGER.
-UH, MR. CAT.
-WHAT IS IT?
-LOVE SHINES MOST BEAUTIFULLY
WHEN YOU FEEL SO STRONGLY
THAT YOU WOULD GIVE UP YOUR LIFE
FOR THAT PERSON, DOESN'T IT?
-IT'S POSSIBLE IT DOES,
BUT LOVE CANNOT KEEP SHINING
FOREVER ON THAT FEELING ALONE.
YOU CAN'T MARRY
ON THAT FEELING ALONE.
-WHAT DO YOU MEAN?
-[ BREATHES DEEPLY ]
[ DOOR OPENS ]
OH, MS. RUE.
HERE TO VISIT HIM?
[ DOOR CLOSES ]
-YES.
-LET'S CAPTURE A SACRIFICE.
-NO.
-HM?
-I'LL TAKE CARE OF THAT.
YOU JUST GO BACK TO YOUR DORM.
-[ CHUCKLES ]
YOU WILL?
-WHAT IS IT?
WHAT'S SO FUNNY?
-NOTHING.
I'M LOOKING FORWARD TO IT.
-AGAIN?
THE ENDING'S BEEN TORN OUT.
MY IMAGINATION?
[ DRUM BEATS RAPIDLY ]
-FAKIR!
-WHAT?
-WHEN PEOPLE SAY DUCK GOES WELL
TOGETHER AND IS LOVEY-DOVEY,
WHAT'S IT MEAN, ZURA?
-WHAT?
DUCK IS? WITH WHOM?
-HUH?
-NEVER MIND.
-WHAT'S IT MEAN, ZURA?
-NO CLUE.
[ DRUM BEATING RAPIDLY ]
-TELL ME!
I WANT TO KNOW, ZURA!
-HEY, KNOCK IT OFF!
-CAN YOU PLEASE BE QUIET?!
-[ SIGHS ] I'M SORRY.
[ BIZET'S "HABANERA" PLAYS ]
-[ GROANS ]
EVEN AS I SPEAK, I GO ON
COMMITTING MORE AND MORE CRIMES.
THE MAIDENS FEAR
TO EVEN APPROACH MY BEAUTY,
THIS BEAUTY THAT'S SO POWERFUL
EVEN MYTHO MUST SWOON.
YES, DEEP DOWN, THEY MUST WANT
TO DRINK, AT THE SIGHT OF ME,
ENOUGH TO SEAR MY IMAGE
INTO THEIR EYES.
ALAS, I CANNOT HOPE
TO SAVE THOSE POOR MAIDENS
FROM THEIR DOLOROUS AFFLICTIONS.
OH, HEAVEN, POUR JUDGMENT
UPON THIS SINNER!
-HERE!
-OLé!
[ BULL MOOS ]
MON AMOUR.
-CAN I HAVE A MOMENT?
-BUT OF COURSE, MADEMOISELLE.
MY HEART IS ALWAYS OPEN
TO YOU LADIES.
-COME.
-WHERE TO?
-TO A PLACE WHERE WE CAN BOTH
PROVE OUR LOVE FOR EACH OTHER.
[ BOTH GASP ]
-THE YEAR HAS GROWN DARKER.
-COULD THIS BE A BATTLE?
-HUH?
[ GASPS ] RUE!
-IT WOULD BE CRUEL
TO POOR FATHER
IF WE DIDN'T GET HIM
A SACRIFICIAL HEART TO EAT SOON.
I'M SICK OF WAITING, AS WELL.
-RUE, WHAT ARE YOU --
[ BROOM CLATTERS ]
-I SMELL BLOOD
ABOUT TO BE SPILLED!
-HUH?
WHERE'S DUCK?
-HEY, SHE WENT AFTER THEM.
-WHAT? NO WAY!
DUCK MUST REALLY LOVE TO BATTLE!
-HUH?
I'M SURE THEY WENT THIS WAY.
[ CROWS CAWING ]
-I SAY...WHAT IS IT YOU WANT TO
DO IN A PLACE LIKE THIS?
-[ CHUCKLES ]
-DO YOU HEAR ME?
-YOU SCARED?
-SCARED?
[ SCOFFS ] AM I SCARED?
MY DEAR, NO WORD IS MORE
UNSUITED TO ME THAN FEAR.
THOUGH, I MUST CONFESS,
IF THERE WERE ONE THING
I ACTUALLY DID FEAR...
[ FINGERS SNAP ]
...IT WOULD HAVE TO BE
MY OWN BEAUTY.
-IF YOU LOSE YOUR HEART,
YOU'LL LOSE THAT FEAR, AS WELL.
[ CHUCKLES ]
I HOPE FATHER WILL BE PLEASED
AND SATISFIED WITH THIS.
-HUH? YOU'LL DO ME THE FAVOR OF
INTRODUCING ME TO YOUR FATHER?
-THAT'S RIGHT.
-BUT ISN'T THIS
A BIT TOO SUDDEN?
AFTER ALL, WE KNOW ALMOST
NOTHING ABOUT EACH OTHER.
WE'RE LIKE STRANGERS.
-IT DOESN'T MATTER.
-UH...
-I DESPERATELY NEED YOU.
-UH...UH...
AAH. AAH!
OH, HOW SHAMEFULLY SINFUL
I HAVE BEEN
TO THINK I WOULD EVER BIND
YOUR HEART TO ME THIS TIGHTLY.
OH, HOW -- HOW TERRIBLE
AND GRIEVOUS A SIN.
NO MORE CAN I ATONE
THROUGH LUKEWARM PUNISHMENTS!
MONTAND, IT'S TIME FOR THAT.
-YES, SIR.
-I DON'T NEED ATONEMENTS.
-UH?
-THAT ISN'T
WHAT I WANT FROM YOU.
-[ SIGHS ]
I UNDERSTAND.
SINCE YOU INSIST, MADEMOISELLE.
-EVEN IF IT'S JUST
FOR ONE NIGHT...
I'LL HAVE YOU ASSUAGE
MY FATHER'S HUNGER.
-TONIGHT, I WILL
OFFER EVERYTHING TO YOU.
-OH, RUE, WHERE ARE YOU?
[ PEOPLE SHOUTING INDISTINCTLY ]
[ FANFARE PLAYS ]
-WHOA!
THAT WAS FEMIO'S -- HM?
[ CROWS CAWING ]
[ GASPS ] THERE.
-PROMISE TO LOVE ONLY ME.
I WANT YOU TO PROMISE ME THAT
YOU WILL HATE EVERYONE ELSE.
-I WILL.
I'LL LOVE ONLY YOU.
YOU AND YOU ALONE.
NO, I CAN'T!
-[ GASPS ]
YES, LOVING JUST ONE WOMAN
IS SOMETHING OF WHICH
I'M INCAPABLE.
AND WHO MIGHT YOU BE,
MADEMOISELLE?
-[ GASPS ]
HE CAN'T. [ GASPS ]
[ GASPS ]
-PLEASE FORGIVE MY RUDENESS,
MADEMOISELLE.
YOUR CHARMS ARE SO ENTICING, SO
ENTHRALLING, I COULDN'T RESIST.
-WAIT.
LET GO OF HIM, KRAEHE.
-WHO ARE YOU?
-PLEASE DANCE WITH ME,
MR. FEMIO.
-WITH YOU?
[ STAMMERING ]
I CAN'T!
I COULDN'T CHOOSE JUST ONE
OF YOU -- SOMETHING SO CRUEL!
[ SOBS ]
[ RUMBLING ]
FOR ME TO TAKE
THIS MUCH OF THE WORLD'S LOVE
STRICTLY FOR MYSELF...
MY SIN IS GREAT, TOO GREAT.
I'VE COMMITTED AN ETERNAL SIN
FOR WHICH I CANNOT ATONE.
-LOOK, SCHOOLYARD GOSSIP
IS NO EDUCATION.
[ GASPS ]
-OH, HEAVEN...
POUR JUDGMENT UPON THIS SINNER!
-HERE!
-O-O-O-O-OL-- AAH!
MON...AMI.
[ GROANS ]
[ WIND RUSTLING ]
-KRAEHE!
KRAEHE.
-COME.
LET US GO, MASTER FEMIO.
[ BULL MOOS ]
[ BULLS MOOING ]
-WHY BULLS?
-WOW, THERE ARE SO MANY, ZURA!
-OH, IT'S DUCK, ZURA!
-HEY, FAKIR.
-DID SOMETHING HAPPEN?
-WELL, NO.
I FEEL KIND OF LIKE
SOMETHING HAPPENED
AND KIND OF LIKE IT DIDN'T.
-HOW DESCRIPTIVE.
-[ LAUGHS ]
UH...SAY, FAKIR.
-YEAH, WHAT?
-WHAT WAS THAT FOR?
-MYTHO DID THIS MIME
IN CLASS TODAY.
I DON'T KNOW WHY HE DID IT.
BUT THAT WAS THE REAL MYTHO,
WASN'T IT?
-ARE YOU LOVEY-DOVEY
WITH MYTHO, ZURA?
-HUH?
-UZURA, MIND YOUR OWN BUSINESS.
-YOU KNEW, DIDN'T YOU?
-KNEW WHAT?
-THAT I'D BE UNABLE TO CAPTURE
A SACRIFICE MYSELF.
-SO, IT DIDN'T GO WELL,
I TAKE IT?
YOU WEREN'T LOVED SO MUCH THAT
HE WOULD GIVE YOU HIS LIFE.
POOR BABY.
-[ GASPS ]
-OH, DEAR.
THE SECOND PRINCESS
IS A PRINCESS WHO ISN'T LOVED
NO MATTER HOW MUCH
SHE CONFESSES HER OWN LOVE.
I GUESS NOTHING EVER GOES
THE WAY YOU WANT IT TO, DOES IT?
[ LAUGHS EVILLY ]
[ RITSUKO OKAZAKI'S "THOUGH
MY LOVE IS SMALL" PLAYS ]
[ WOMAN SINGING IN JAPANESE ]
-DO YOU THINK IT'S POSSIBLE
TO TURN A LOVE THAT'S BEEN MADE
IMPURE BACK TO NORMAL?
-RIGHT NOW, I WANT YOU
TO STICK TO MYTHO
AS CLOSE AS YOU CAN
SO THAT WAY --
-A WANDERING KNIGHT
UNABLE TO DO ANYTHING?
I THINK THE ROLE FITS YOU
TO A "T," FAKIR.
-MAYBE HE'S PREPARING A PLACE
FOR ME TO DIE.
-YOUR SWORD IS SEEKING BLOOD,
ISN'T IT?
CUT DOWN THAT USELESS EXCUSE
FOR A KNIGHT.
-STOP!
PLEASE, FAKIR, DO NOT BITE.
-ALL YOU CHILDREN WHO LOVE
STORIES, COME, GATHER 'ROUND.
[ LAUGHS EVILLY ]