-ONCE UPON A TIME,
THERE WAS A MAN
WHO FELL IN LOVE WITH A DOLL.
PERHAPS THE MAN'S LOVE
MADE ITSELF FELT.
FOR ONE DAY, THE DOLL CAME
TO LIFE AND BEGAN TO DANCE.
THE MAN WAS DELIGHTED.
HE THOUGHT A DOLL
WOULD NEVER BETRAY HIS LOVE
AND THAT NOW HE COULD
HAVE THE WORLD'S
MOST PURE AND INNOCENT LOVE
ALL TO HIMSELF.
UNFORTUNATELY FOR HIM,
THE DOLL WHO HAD BEEN GIVEN LIFE
REJECTED THE MAN'S LOVE
AND FELL IN LOVE
WITH ANOTHER MAN.
[ RITSUKO OKAZAKI'S
"MORNING GRACE" PLAYS ]
-[ SINGING IN JAPANESE ]
[ SINGING CONTINUES ]
[ TCHAIKOVSKY'S "FINAL
WALTZ AND APOTHEOSIS" FROM
"THE NUTCRACKER" PLAYS ]
[ BIRDS CHIRPING ]
-OH, I COULDN'T SLEEP.
MYTHO...
I WONDER WHY HE DID THAT.
FOR HIM TO JUMP OUT
OF THE WINDOW LIKE THAT,
COULD IT BE 'CAUSE HIS HEART
HASN'T BEEN
COMPLETELY RETURNED YET?
THEN I'VE GOT TO TRY
EVEN HARDER
TO GET THE REST OF HIS HEART
BACK FOR HIM AND DO IT QUICKLY!
-WHAT THE HELL HAPPENED?
-MYTHO WAS CALLED
INTO THE OFFICE!
-THIS IS SERIOUS!
-HUH?
-NO WAY!
-SENIOR FAKIR?
-HE WAS CALLED TO!
-OH, MUST BE
FOR THE PUSHING INCIDENT.
-HUH, PUSHING IN--
-YOU DON'T KNOW, DUCK?
THE WONDERFUL FAKIR PUSHED THE
WONDERFUL AND UNRESISTING MYTHO
OUT OF THE WINDOW!
-WHAT?!
THERE'S GOT TO BE SOME KIND
OF MISTAKE
'CAUSE MYTHO JUMPED OUT HIMSELF!
IT WASN'T --
-AS IF HE'D DO THAT.
-EVERYONE WAS WATCHING,
SO EXCUSES WON'T WORK.
-BUT IT...
-THAT WAS JUST TOO CRUEL,
EVEN FOR FAKIR.
-OH, I HOPE HE BECOMES
A FULL-FLEDGED CRIMINAL
AND PLUNGES HEADLONG
DOWN THE PATH
TO BECOMING ONE OF LIFE'S
LOSERS!
-ANYWAY, LET'S GO SEE!
-YES, LET'S!
-[ Thinking ] BUT WHEN
I SAW HIM, I'M SURE THAT HE...
[ GRUNTING ]
-SHH!
-OH.
FINE, THEN!
[ WHISTLE! ]
QUACK!
[ SPARKLE! ]
QUACK, QUACK, QUACK, QUACK,
QUACK, QUACK, QUACK, QUACK!
-UNPLEASANT INCIDENTS JUST KEEP
HAPPENING LATELY, DON'T THEY?
WHAT EXACTLY HAPPENED YESTERDAY?
-[ GRUNTING ]
THAT WAS SIMPLY DUE
TO MY CARELESSNESS.
-WHAT?
-JUST AN ACCIDENT.
-[ GASPS ]
-ACCIDENT?
-YES.
I'M SORRY TO HAVE CAUSED
YOU WORRY.
-WHY WOULD YOU LIE LIKE THAT?
-WHAT DO YOU MEAN, MR. FAKIR?
I MUST SAY,
I AM RELUCTANT TO ACCEPT
THE ACCIDENT EXPLANATION MYSELF.
-ARE YOU SAYING YOU BELIEVE
THAT FAKIR PUSHED ME
OUT OF THE WINDOW, MR. CAT?
-ARGUMENTS CAN SOMETIMES
HAPPEN, MR. MYTHO.
FOR EXAMPLE,
ALBRECHT AND HILARION
BOTH WANTED TO MARRY
THE MAIDEN GISELLE!
[ GROWLS ]
THEIR DESIRE
TO MARRY HER CAUSED THEM TO...
[ SCREAMS ]
[ GROANS ]
I SUPPOSE YOU'RE A LITTLE YOUNG
FOR THAT PARTICULAR PROBLEM.
WELL, THAT'S FINE,
BUT I CANNOT LET YOU CONTINUE
TO LIVE IN ONE ROOM!
-THEN I WILL --
-I WILL LEAVE.
-FAKIR...
[ ALL SCREAM ]
-QUITE AUDACIOUS OF YOU
TO BE EAVESDROPPING ON ME!
KEEP IT UP,
AND I'LL HAVE YOU MARRY --
[ ALL SCREAM ]
[ SIGHS ]
-QUACK.
-[ SLURPING, PURRING ]
-[ GASPS ]
-[ CHUCKLES ]
-[ GASPS ] THOSE EYES AGAIN.
WHAT'S HAPPENED TO YOU, MYTHO?
-HE LOOKS LIKE HE'S IN PAIN.
-WELL, HE WAS BETRAYED
BY THE PERSON
HE THOUGHT WAS HIS BEST FRIEND.
-I BET HE COVERED
FOR SENIOR FAKIR ANYWAY.
-THAT'S SO LIKE HIM.
-[ GROANS ]
-QUACK! OH.
-WHO ARE YOU?
-HUH?
-WHY --
WHY ARE YOU INSIDE OF ME?
-[ Thinking ]
WHO IS HE TALKING TO?
[ FOOTSTEPS APPROACH ]
-UH...
-PIKE?
-UM, YOU KNOW, THIS MIGHT BE
NONE OF MY BUSINESS,
BUT I THINK
YOU'RE MAKING A BIG MISTAKE.
I'M TALKING ABOUT SENIOR FAKIR.
YOU TWO HAVE BEEN FRIENDS
FOR A LONG TIME,
SO IT'S NOT
THAT I DON'T UNDERSTAND
WHY YOU'D WANT TO COVER FOR HIM
IN FRONT OF MR. CAT,
BUT IF SOMETHING
LIKE THIS HAPPENS A SECOND TIME,
YOU MIGHT END UP NEVER BEING
ABLE TO DANCE AGAIN OR WORSE.
-WHY ARE YOU TALKING TO ME
ABOUT THIS?
-UH, YESTERDAY, I SAW YOU.
I SAW YOU GLIDING DOWN
FROM THE SKY
WITH THIS ENORMOUS WHITE BIRD
NEXT TO YOU.
-UH...
-WHEN I SAW THAT...
I THOUGHT MAYBE YOU
WERE BEING PROTECTED
BY, LIKE, THE GOD OF DANCE
OR SOMETHING.
-[ Thinking ] WHITE BIRD.
DOES SHE MEAN TUTU?
-YOU SAY SUCH CUTE THINGS, PIKE,
AND YOU HAVE A FORTHRIGHT,
STEADFAST,
AND BEAUTIFUL HEART BEATING
WITHIN YOU.
-[ GASPS ]
UH...
UH, EXCUSE ME! I HAVE TO GO!
-PIKE...
-[ GIGGLES ]
I SAW THAT, I SAW THAT!
-OH.
QUACK.
[ GASPS ]
HE'S GONE.
A CROW'S FEATHER?
IS THIS...
I KNOW. I'LL GO TALK TO FAKIR!
ANYWAY, I HAVE TO TURN BACK
INTO A GIRL SOMEWHERE.
[ INDISTINCT CONVERSATIONS ]
[ BEEP! BEEP! BEEP! ]
NO GOOD -- TOO MANY PEOPLE.
I GOT IT.
THIS PLACE SHOULD BE OKAY.
[ SPLASH! ]
[ SPARKLE! ]
-[ GRUNTING ]
MAN, I REALLY
DANCED MY BUTT OFF.
[ SIGHS ]
HUH, HUH?
HUH?
OH, WHERE DID DYLAN GO?
-UH-OH.
-MR. ARMADYLAN!
-YES, SIR.
[ DOOR CLOSES ]
-OH!
HE SCARED ME!
WAIT, THERE'S NO TIME
FOR WORRYING!
I WONDER WHERE FAKIR IS.
OH!
-HEY, IS SOMETHING
GOING ON WITH HIM?
-WITH FAKIR.
-HE'S ACTING WEIRD.
-HE'S UP IN THE LIBRARY.
-HOLED UP IN THERE.
-LIBRARY?
HMM.
HE'S REALLY HERE!
HEY, FAKIR, JUST NOW,
MYTHO AND PIKE --
AND IT WAS REALLY WEIRD,
AND MYTHO WAS --
AND WHAT HAPPENED YESTERDAY
WAS WEIRD, TOO,
AND I THOUGHT MEOWSINSKI'S
SHOES MIGHT BE MYTHO'S FAULT,
BUT THAT COULD JUST
BE MY IMAGINATION.
BUT -- BUT -- BUT IT REALLY
WAS SUPER WEIRD, SO MYTHO WAS --
-CAN YOU PLEASE BE
A LITTLE QUIETER?
-MYTHO! OH, I'M SORRY.
-CALM DOWN.
-MM.
DID SOMETHING HAPPEN TO MYTHO?
-THAT'S WHAT I'M TRYING
TO FIND OUT.
-AND WHAT HAPPENED YESTERDAY?
MYTHO JUMPED OUT THE WINDOW
HIMSELF, DIDN'T HE?
BUT IN FRONT OF MR. CAT,
HE MADE IT SOUND LIKE
HE WAS JUST COVERING FOR YOU,
AND THAT MADE IT LOOK LIKE
YOU WERE THE BAD GUY.
[ BOOK CLOSES ]
OH, AND JUST NOW,
I WAS FOLLOWING MYTHO AROUND
TO SEE WHAT WAS UP,
AND THEN HE VANISHED
ALL OF A SUDDEN.
HE LEFT BEHIND...
...A CROW'S FEATHER.
-WHAT?!
-HUH?
-OH!
WHY DID YOU STOP?
OH.
-[ CHUCKLES ]
-IT'S RUE! FAKIR?
FAKIR!
-YOU DID THIS!
WHAT DID YOU DO TO MYTHO?
-WHAT DO YOU MEAN?
-DON'T PLAY DUMB WITH ME!
-LET GO OF ME! THAT HURTS!
-SHOW YOUR TRUE COLORS!
KRAEHE.
-[ CHUCKLES ]
-STOP IT.
-LET GO OF ME!
[ SLAP! ]
[ ALL GASP ]
-DON'T WORRY ABOUT ME.
I'LL BE JUST FINE.
-SO LIKE MYTHO.
-HE'S INCREDIBLY MATURE.
-AS MUCH AS FAKIR'S IMMATURE.
-OH, DEAR.
DUCK'S PRINCE IS CHANGING
AND NOT FOR THE BETTER,
I'M AFRAID.
DO SOMETHING FAST, LITTLE DUCK,
BEFORE THE BEAUTIFUL SPARKLE
IN THE EYES UNDER THAT EVIL MASK
FADES COMPLETELY.
[ TCHAIKOVSKY'S
"NUTCRACKER: MARCH" PLAYS ]
-[ GROANS ]
-ARE YOU IN PAIN, FATHER?
I WANT TO LEAVE THIS PLACE
AS SOON AS I CAN.
IF I WERE FREE,
I COULD WRAP THESE WINGS
AROUND MY DEAR DAUGHTER
AND HUG HER AS MUCH AS I WANTED.
-YOU ONLY NEED ENDURE
IT A LITTLE LONGER, FATHER.
IT LOOKS LIKE THE PRINCE
HAS FOUND US OUR PREY.
-THE PRINCE HAS?
OH.
-I'M SO GLAD I OBEYED
YOUR INSTRUCTIONS, FATHER.
YES.
IF I HAD NOT SOAKED THE HEART
SHARD WITH THE FEELING OF LOVE
AND FATHER'S BLOOD
THAT DAY LIKE HE TOLD ME TO,
MY PRINCE WOULD NOT HAVE
RETURNED TO ME.
I HAVE TO BE GRATEFUL
TO PRINCESS TUTU
FOR GIVING THE HEART SHARD BACK
TO HIM.
-IT WOULD SERVE YOU WELL, ALSO,
TO BE ACCOMMODATING
TO PRINCESS TUTU.
IN ORDER TO BREAK THE SEAL
TO RELEASE ME,
WE HAVE TO FIND THE REST
OF THE PRINCE'S HEART SHARDS.
WE NEED PRINCESS TUTU'S POWER
TO DO THAT.
IF YOU TRY TO GET
RID OF HER AGAIN,
I'LL SHOW YOU NO MERCY,
DAUGHTER OR NOT!
-I'M SORRY! I WON'T, FATHER!
-GOOD!
-HEY, THERE, RUE.
-OTHER THAN MYSELF, NO ONE
BUT THE PRINCE IN THE STORY
CAN TRULY LOVE
A PITIFUL PERSON LIKE YOU,
WHO, DESPITE BEING A CROW,
HAD BEEN BORN
INTO THIS HIDEOUS HUMAN BODY.
I AM SURE WE WOULD BOTH LIKE
TO SEE YOUR WEDDING DAY
AS SOON AS POSSIBLE.
-THANK YOU, FATHER.
-I FEEL LIKE THAT DAY
WAS SUCH A LONG TIME AGO.
-DUCK!
HAPPY NEWS!
-OH, WHAT?
-WELL, I JUST HEARD
STARTING TOMORROW,
THE WONDERFUL FAKIR IS SUSPENDED
FROM SCHOOL FOR A WHOLE WEEK!
-NO WAY!
-YES WAY!
AT THIS RATE, HE'LL GRADUATE
FROM JUVIE TO FELON IN NO TIME!
-FAKIR WAS...
-MORE IMPORTANTLY...
-OH.
-...JUST NOW WHILE I JUST
HAPPENED TO BE FOLLOWING PIKE,
I JUST HAPPENED TO SEE
HER MEET UP WITH MYTHO,
AND AS I JUST HAPPENED TO
KEEP FOLLOWING THEM,
THEY WENT OFF TO A PLACE
WHERE THERE WAS ABSOLUTELY
NO ONE AROUND.
[ GIGGLES ]
-PIKE WAS WITH MYTHO?
-WELL, WANT TO
IT JUST HAPPENED TO GO SEE?
-MM.
-THAT'S THE SPIRIT!
[ BIRDS CHIRPING ]
SEE?
-[ GASPS ]
-PIKE...
[ BOING! BOING! BOING! BOING!
WHISTLE! ]
-HEY, HOLD ON!
-DUCK, WHAT'S --
WHAT ARE YOU DOING?
-UM, UH, YOU SEE --
-WHAT'S WRONG?
YOU HAVE A PROBLEM WITH THIS?
JUST WHAT DO YOU CARE
IF MYTHO AND I ARE DATING?
THAT'S OUR BUSINESS!
-WHAT?
MYTHO, YOU LIKE PIKE?
[ Thinking ] THOSE EYES AGAIN.
MYTHO, WHAT'S HAPPENED TO YOU?
SOMETHING'S WEIRD HERE.
-WHAT'S SO WEIRD
ABOUT GOING OUT WITH ME?!
-NO, THAT'S NOT WHAT I MEANT!
I MEANT YESTERDAY AND STUFF.
MYTHO JUMPED OUT THE WINDOW
HIMSELF, BUT --
-HUH?
-YOU'RE STILL SAYING THAT?!
-AND MR. CAT'S SHOES.
MYTHO MIGHT'VE --
-WILL YOU CUT IT OUT ALREADY?!
-HUH?
-MYTHO.
-JUST WHO...ARE YOU?
WHAT ARE YOU TRYING
TO MAKE ME DO?
-UH...MYTHO, WAIT!
-STAY AWAY!
-MYTHO, WHY?
-AW, IT WAS JUST
GETTING GOOD, TOO.
[ KNOCK ON DOOR ]
-HEY, PIKE, PLEASE COME OUT!
-YEAH, LET'S TAKE
THIS OUTSIDE RIGHT NOW!
-WE CAN TALK PEACEFULLY, OKAY?
-WE ARE GONNA STRAIGHTEN
A FEW THINGS OUT!
-SORRY, BUT BE QUIET
FOR A SECOND.
-HUH? BUT YOU HAVE TO TAKE A
HARSHER TONE WITH YOUR ENEMIES.
-LILIE, I DON'T THINK OF PIKE
AS AN ENEMY.
-UH, REALLY?
DUCK, IS THIS REALLY OKAY?
-UH-HUH. THAT'S HOW I FEEL.
-HEY, SHE SAYS AS AN ENEMY,
YOU'RE NOT WORTH THINKING ABOUT!
-NO, THAT ISN'T WHAT I MEANT!
[ LAUGHS ]
-THAT'S ENOUGH FOR TODAY!
LET'S GO!
-WE'LL LET YOU OFF
WITH THIS FOR TODAY!
[ LAUGHS MANICALLY ]
-UH...
MYTHO?
[ DOOR OPENS ]
- [ CHUCKLES ]
-KRAEHE?
-YOU'RE WORKING INTENTLY.
IS THE SUBJECT OF YOUR RESEARCH
PRINCES, OR IS IT RAVENS?
SHALL I TELL YOU WHAT THE PRINCE
IS MOVING TOWARDS BECOMING?
-SO YOU DID DO SOMETHING.
-THE HEART SHARD OF LOVE THAT
PRINCESS TUTU GAVE BACK TO HIM,
THAT SHARD WAS SOAKED IN A BATH
OF THE RAVEN'S BLOOD, SO...
-THE RAVEN'S BLOOD? THEN YOU --
-MY FATHER WAS WILLING TO PART
WITH SOME OF HIS OWN BLOOD
FOR THE SAKE OF HIS DAUGHTER.
-THE RAVEN'S DAUGHTER?
-THE PRINCE WILL SOON CHANGE.
HE'LL LOVE ONLY ME,
AND HE'LL FIND A YOUNG AND
BEAUTIFUL HEART FOR MY FATHER
AND OFFER IT UP TO HIM
AS A SACRIFICE.
WHEN THE BLOOD HAS FINISHED
PERMEATING HIS WHOLE HEART,
HE WILL NEVER GO BACK
TO THE WAY HE WAS.
-DID YOU TELL TUTU
ABOUT ALL THIS?
-I SHOULD.
IF I DID THAT, I COULD MAKE
HER SUFFER, COULDN'T I?
OR PERHAPS IT
WOULD BE MORE EFFECTIVE
TO TELL THE PRINCE
THAT SHE IS, IN TRUTH,
A GIRL WHO IS REALLY
A WRETCHED EXCUSE FOR A DANCER.
[ CHUCKLES ]
IT WAS STUPID OF YOU
TO BREAK THE PRINCE'S SWORD.
WITHOUT THAT BLADE,
YOU CAN'T EVEN HOPE TO TAKE
HIS HEART OUT NOW, CAN YOU?
BUT YOU'RE ONLY HUMAN,
AFTER ALL.
MAYBE ALL YOU CAN DO
IS LOOK THINGS UP IN BOOKS.
[ LAUGHS ]
-[ GASPS ]
PIKE.
-SORRY ABOUT BEFORE.
I TRULY AND HONESTLY
NEED YOUR LOVE.
-ALL RIGHT, MM.
-ARE YOU AFRAID?
-NO, O-OF COURSE NOT.
-PIKE, PROMISE TO LOVE ONLY ME.
-ALL RIGHT.
-PROMISE ME THAT YOU'LL HATE
EVERYONE ELSE.
-I WILL.
I PROMISE TO LOVE ONLY YOU
AND TO HATE EVERYONE ELSE, TOO.
-PIKE.
-ALL RIGHT, AS PROOF THEN...
YOU'LL GIVE ME
YOUR BEAUTIFUL HEART.
WON'T YOU?
-YES.
-THEN STEP FORWARD.
INTO MY ARMS!
GIVE ME YOUR HEART!
-GIVE ME YOUR HEART!
-[ GASPS ]
[ CLASSICAL MUSIC PLAYS ]
-THAT'S THE WALTZ OF THE DOLL.
IT'S FROM "COPPéLIA."
-IF I CAN JUST HAVE MYTHO,
I DON'T MIND LOSING MY HEART
AND TURNING INTO A DOLL.
-THE MORE BEAUTIFUL THE HEART,
THE STRONGER THE FRAGRANCE
WHEN IT'S DYED IN EVIL!
- DIDN'T MYTHO FALL IN LOVE
WITH PIKE?
NO, HE MUSTN'T TAKE
PIKE'S HEART!
[ SPARKLE! BUBBLE! BUBBLE! ]
[ SPARKLE! SPARKLE! SPARKLE!
SPARKLE! SPARKLE! ]
[ SPARKLE! SPARKLE! ]
[ MUSIC CONTINUES ]
WAIT, PLEASE COME DANCE WITH ME.
WON'T YOU, PIKE?
-NO.
-TUTU.
[ GRUNTS ]
-OH! PIKE! AGH!
-YOUR PLEAS ARE USELESS.
PIKE HERSELF WANTS
TO GIVE HER HEART TO ME
AND BECOME A SACRIFICE.
AS LONG AS HER FEELINGS
STAY THIS WAY --
-PIKE, STOP!
-IS THIS TRULY WHAT YOU DESIRE?
SWANHILDE FROM "COPPéLIA"
WAS A NORMAL GIRL
MERELY PRETENDING TO BE A DOLL.
JUST LIKE YOU, PIKE --
A GIRL WHO LIKES CHATTING,
SINGING, AND LOVES DANCING.
A GIRL DEEPLY IN LOVE.
IF YOU REALLY LOVE MYTHO,
THEN YOU MUST WANT
TO CHAT WITH HIM AND SING
AND DANCE WITH HIM, RIGHT?
YOU SAY YOU DON'T MIND
LOSING YOUR HEART,
BUT THAT'S NOT THE REAL YOU!
-UH...
-OH.
-TUTU.
-MYTHO.
-IS THIS ALL A BAD DREAM?
-MYTHO...
-HE'S...
-WHAT?
-ANOTHER ME INSIDE ME IS...
TUTU,
WHAT'S GOING TO HAPPEN TO ME?
-[ GASPS ]
-I...
-MYTHO...
-[ SNORING ]
HMM?
[ DOOR OPENS ]
-GOOD MORNING, PRINCESSES.
[ DOOR CLOSES ]
-HEY, WHAT HAPPENED?
-OH, YOU DON'T REMEMBER?
DUCK DRAGGED YOU HOME LATE LAST
NIGHT AND PUT YOU INTO BED.
-HUH?
-THE TWO OF YOU MUST'VE HAD A
MAGNIFICENT, SPECTACULAR BATTLE!
OH, HOW I WISH I'D SEEN IT,
BOTH OF YOU ABANDONING
FRIENDSHIP TO FIGHT,
TWO GIRLS IN LOVE WITH MYTHO!
-ME IN LOVE WITH MYTHO?!
OH, YEAH, COME TO THINK OF IT,
I GUESS I WAS, HUH?
-PIKE, THANK GOODNESS.
-SO, HOW'D YOU TWO FIGHT?
-WE DIDN'T!
-WHAT?!
YOU GOT TO BE KIDDING ME!
-BUT, MAN, TO BE HONEST...
I DON'T EVEN KNOW MYSELF
WHY I WAS SO CRAZY ABOUT MYTHO
IN THE FIRST PLACE.
OH!
THAT MUST BE WHAT YOU
CALL THE RASHNESS OF YOUTH!
I'M STICKING TO FAKIR LOVE
FROM NOW ON!
-PRINCESS TUTU IS THE ONLY ONE
WHO CAN GET BACK
THE PRINCE'S HEART,
BUT WHO CAN TURN THE HEART
SOAKED IN RAVEN'S BLOOD
BACK TO NORMAL?
WILL PRINCESS TUTU BE ABLE
TO DO THAT?
[ SLOW MUSIC PLAYS ]
-[ SINGING IN JAPANESE ]
[ SINGING IN JAPANESE
CONTINUES ]
-IS SOMETHING HAPPENING BEHIND
THE SCENES WHERE I CAN'T SEE IT?
I DON'T WANT TO FIGHT ANYMORE.
-IT WOULD BE WONDERFUL
IF THE WORLD WERE
FULL OF FLOWERS, WOULDN'T IT?
-YOUR BEAUTIFUL HEART
MAKES BEAUTIFUL FLOWERS BLOOM.
-I WAS LOOKING FOR A TAIL,
AND I FOUND HER BUTT, ZURA!
-WELL, HER NAME IS UZURA.
KARON MADE HER FROM THE WOOD
FROM EDEL THAT DIDN'T BURN UP.
-KRAEHE,
WHAT HAVE YOU DONE TO MYTHO?
-THE ONE WHO MADE THE PRINCE
LIKE THIS IS YOU, TUTU.
-WHY?! WHY WON'T YOU LOVE ME?!
-ALL YOU CHILDREN WHO LOVE
STORIES, COME GATHER 'ROUND.
[ LAUGHS EVILLY ]