‐ [Narrator] Once upon a time,
there was a man who died.
The story was interrupted.
Along with his heart,
the prince lost
his kindness towards
other people,
and even him memories of
having fought bravely.
Meanwhile, scattered
throughout the town,
the shards of the prince's
heart sought places to settle,
and found their way
into people's hearts,
which had a void in them.
Among those possessed
by the shards
were some that ended up making
their own tales go awry.
(gentle piano music)
‐ [Duck] I really and
truly have been able
to become Princess Tutu.
‐ Tuck your chin in!
(laughing)
It's no laughing matter!
If you can't even do that,
then you'll never
get off probation!
‐ Stop it!
Now be reasonable!
Duck simply isn't capable
of doing two things at once!
‐ All she has to do is walk
with a book on her head!
‐ But something so simple,
she can't do it,
she simply can't!
‐ Then she'll never
be a prima ballerina!
‐ No she won't, she couldn't
possibly become one.
Stop saying such awful things!
Oh, look how hurt she is.
(whimpering)
Come on, smile.
‐ Hey, it's your fault.
‐ No way.
‐ But for someone on probation,
Duck sure has been acting weird,
and goofy smiley all day.
‐ She's always been weird.
‐ I mean more than usual.
‐ Now that you say it.
‐ What?
‐ [Both] Did
something happen, huh?
‐ [Duck] No, not really.
‐ [Both] Liar!
‐ [Duck] Not that there
was anything, but.
‐ [Both] So there was!
‐ [Duck] Uh, well.
‐ [Both] Come on
Duck, spit it out!
‐ Um, so yeah, this dream,
it's about this one
dream that I had.
See, there's this really strong
and handsome prince in it.
And this prince is fighting
against and evil raven.
He conceals the raven away
as he shatters his own heart.
But when he loses his heart,
he also loses his feelings.
And the prince's eyes
always look so lonely.
‐ Is that all?
Hey, I've heard a
story like that before.
‐ Story?
‐ It's from the
Prince and the Raven.
‐ Huh?
‐ Here, this book, right?
‐ The prince was a hero who
fought the demonic raven.
Well, he was when they were
still inside the story.
‐ [Duck] And, what's
the name of the guy
who wrote the story?
‐ His name?
It's Drosselmeyer,
don't you know?
‐ No, I had no idea!
‐ This is no time for silly
books and stupid grins.
‐ Two books are too
much for you, Duck.
‐ Make sure you can do
it by the end of the day!
‐ Good luck, you've
got nothing to lose!
‐ And don't you dare slack off!
‐ Oh, so this
Drosselmeyer person,
does he lives
somewhere in this town?
‐ Huh?
No way, he died ages ago.
‐ What?
‐ The story ends part
of the way through, too.
‐ Oh yeah, didn't he like,
die while he was writing
the book or something?
‐ What?
‐ Yes, he came out
of the story I wrote
and ended up losing his
heart to seal the raven away.
‐ That means the person
writing the story died
and the characters in
the story came out?
Something that strange.
But I guess it isn't as strange
as a duck turning into a person.
So that would mean
that senior Mytho
is actually a prince
out of a story.
That must be why he's
so handsome then.
It's Rue.
I wonder if she
knows about this.
Oh, it's senior Mytho!
So, he's going on
a picnic with Rue.
Lucky her.
But you know, when you
get right down to it,
I'm just a duck.
Maybe I'll practice
or something.
‐ Hey!
(gasps)
Have you seen Mytho around?
‐ Is something the
matter with senior Mytho?
‐ He went out, without
even telling me about it.
‐ Gee, who cares about that?
He's Rue's boyfriend, after all.
‐ (gasps) What?
So he's with Rue?
Were did they go?
Tell me!
‐ I don't know!
‐ Don't lie to me!
‐ It's the truth!
Oh, I wonder if he knows
about senior Mytho.
Say, do you happen
to know the story
of the Prince and the Raven?
‐ What about it?
‐ [Duck] Oh, um,
nothing really about it.
‐ A tale for children
and nothing more.
‐ Hm, acting so high and mighty.
He doesn't even have a clue.
So senior Mytho is a
prince from inside a story,
and I'm the only one
who knows about it.
It's up to me to
protect my prince.
(bells chiming)
I'm not playing hooky,
I'm just taking a break.
I'm allowed to do that.
Besides, if I see
senior Mytho and Rue,
I can tell them that nasty
guy was looking for them.
I wonder if it's
okay to tell them.
‐ [Edel] Truth is
a shy little thing.
If you approach, it will hide.
‐ Miss Edel?
‐ Truth is a lonesome
little thing.
If you run away,
it will give chase.
Having doubts, are you?
‐ Well, um, I am.
So you see, there's this person,
and then there's another person
who's really good
friends with that person,
and that person also
has another good friend,
but that person's friends
aren't exactly friends
with one another.
Do you understand what
I'm trying to say?
‐ A mighty wind can fan
flames and make treetops sway,
but flames burn
trees to the ground.
‐ So, wind and flames
and trees, huh?
Does that mean
that they can never
get along with each other?
‐ Who's to say?
‐ Huh.
But if the wind was too strong,
it would put out the fire
and topple all the trees.
So that means, I don't get it.
Well, thanks anyway Miss Edel!
Hm, if it's a picnic,
maybe they're at this park.
Hey, there they are!
‐ Mytho.
‐ [Mytho] What?
‐ I want to hear you
say that you love me.
(yelps)
‐ Oh, what should I do?
Should I go back?
I should go back, shouldn't I?
I'm going back now.
‐ Yes Rue, I love you.
‐ [Rue] Really?
‐ [Mytho] I really love you.
‐ I'm feeling thirsty.
(classical piano music)
‐ Huh?
‐ I think I would like
to drink some water.
Get it for me?
‐ Yes.
‐ (whimpering) He's
coming this way.
What do I do?
He might see me!
Man, they really are
perfect for each other.
But they didn't look
like they were having
very much fun out there.
If he said something
like that to me.
Like that.
‐ Hello, Duck.
(Duck giggles)
You know I love you, don't you?
I really do.
(Duck giggles)
‐ Ow!
Excuse.
Oh, senior Mytho.
Hello!
Um, the weather's
pretty nice today, huh?
So it may be bright
during the day
but I'm sure it'll
be dark at night.
Stupid me, what am I
stating the obvious for,
I gotta say something funny!
Uh, you know what?
I really love taking walks,
and you really love Rue, right?
Oh man, what the
heck am I saying?
‐ [Mytho] Probably.
‐ Probably?
‐ I guess I don't really
understand what love is.
But Rue and Fakir
are the only ones
who will tell me
what to do, so I...
‐ You don't understand love?
Senior Mytho?
‐ Mytho's fine.
‐ (screaming) Oh, senior Mytho!
I mean Mytho, your hand!
Does it hurt?
‐ No.
So then why the weird face?
‐ Is it really a weird face?
(whimpers) But
you're hurt, Mytho!
‐ Fakir and Rue don't
say things like that.
‐ It's the prince's eyes.
The poor prince
who lost his heart.
That's why he doesn't
know his own feelings,
not even about
loving or hurting.
Then I'll do my best!
‐ At what?
‐ Um, that is,
nothing in particular,
but rather, I wanna work super
hard at all sorts of things!
Right, that injury!
It'll get worse if you
don't wash it properly.
Thank goodness it's
nothing too bad.
(screams) The water
that you went and got.
I'm sorry, I'm really sorry,
I'll go get some more.
That being said, river
water just wouldn't cut it.
Rue deserves good‐tasting
water, after all.
Water from these houses
wouldn't work either, right?
Where should I get it from?
Oh, am I not in town?
Guess I must have
walked too far.
Oh, Mytho!
I'll just go get the water,
so you just stay here
and I'll be right back!
Wait, I mean, where
can I find water?
‐ Oh, right there.
‐ Oh, that's a restaurant!
Some restaurant water
would be perfect, huh?
‐ Maybe.
‐ Open, Ebine.
I wonder if that's
the restaurant's name.
(knocking)
Excuse me!
‐ Yes?
‐ Uh, this is a
restaurant, right?
‐ Yes, yes it is!
(screaming)
One moment, please!
(crashing)
Thank you for waiting.
Welcome!
I am the owner and
chef here at Ebine!
How did you find out
about this place?
Did a friend tell you?
‐ [Duck] No.
‐ Then did you go out
of your way to find it?
‐ No, not at all.
‐ It wasn't pure
chance now, huh?
‐ Oh, yeah.
‐ How very splendid!
I've never had a customer
like that before.
Now please, sit down.
‐ Ma'am, I'm not a customer.
‐ Not a customer?
‐ I came for water.
‐ Just for some water?
‐ That is, I'm so sorry!
‐ You're hungry, aren't you?
Then why not have a nice
meal while you're here?
‐ What?
I don't have any money!
‐ That's fine, it
doesn't matter!
Oh yes, I just made
some shrimp pate.
‐ The pendant glowed just now.
Does that mean she has one
of the shards with her?
(Nutcracker Theme music)
‐ Where did Mytho go?
‐ I don't know.
‐ Don't ever take him
out without telling me.
‐ Mytho doesn't belong to you.
‐ Nor to you.
Mytho made mention of a feeling.
‐ What's that?
‐ Where is Mytho?
‐ He went for some water,
and hasn't come back yet.
‐ By himself?
‐ Who else would
he be going with?
This isn't like you at all.
What are you so frantic about?
Wait!
It you're going
to look for Mytho,
then I'm coming with you.
‐ Now!
Please help yourselves to it!
‐ Ma'am, if you could get us‐
‐ Some more?
You're right, this
is hardly enough!
‐ Wait, that's not it!
I have to check and see whether
she has a heart chart or not.
Hm?
It's cold.
So's this, and this and this!
Why are they all cold?
There's not much
taste to them either.
But they look so good.
‐ Rainbow trout!
‐ This one looks warm.
Cold!
‐ And now, rabbit cream stew,
piping hot dumpling salad,
grilled pork shanks.
‐ (whimpers) They're cold, why?
Hey, don't you think
something's strange here?
‐ Like?
‐ Like, all the dishes
she brings out are cold.
Or why she's
feeding us for free!
‐ Who knows?
‐ I see.
Mytho can't even tell
when something's strange.
‐ Here's dessert!
(whimpering)
And that concludes course A.
Next up, course B!
‐ What?
Okay, listen.
I'm going to the restroom.
‐ Sure.
‐ All right, I better
hurry up and check.
‐ (laughing) Yes, that's right.
It's been so long since
we had a customer.
They're eating so much, but
I have to have them eat more!
Who will taste
better, you or you?
‐ Who will taste better?
(whimpering) Grave.
What should I do?
At this rate I'll be...
(dinging)
I don't care what happens to me!
But Mytho, I gotta save him!
I know a story that
goes like this.
A brother and sister
lost in the forest
find a gingerbread house.
Then a kind old woman appears
and serves them
all sorts of food.
But she was really planning
to fatten up the two
and eat them afterwards.
‐ Really.
‐ It's no good, Mytho doesn't
understand he's in danger.
We gotta get out!
Recipes?
And a photograph?
What are these?
‐ What are you doing?
‐ Oh, well, I was
thinking of going soon.
‐ No, you can't!
I've still got my
dishes to cook!
‐ Your dishes?
‐ More must be eaten!
Much more!
‐ Eating more for what?
‐ You'll stay 'til you're done!
‐ Why should I stay
when I'm already full?
‐ I see.
Well then, how about you?
You'll eat more, right?
‐ Probably.
(screaming)
(knocking)
‐ Open up, please open up!
‐ [Ebine] If you won't
eat, you can go home!
‐ Locked.
Oh Mytho!
‐ Come now, it's going awry.
The story's going awry.
Heart shards make their homes
in the holes in people's hearts,
and convolute their stories.
It seems a heart
that is too pure
is an awfully heavy burden.
Now, do tell me,
how will you handle this
story, Princess Tutu?
(magical classical music)
‐ That little
nuisance is gone now.
You just keep eating.
Who could that be?
Who's there?
‐ Meal time has now ended.
Please, my prince,
you must rest a while.
‐ My customer!
Give me back my customer!
‐ Please come dance
with me, Miss Ebine.
‐ I am not a dancer.
My job is not to dance.
My job is to cook, and have
my customers eat my cooking.
‐ What do you hope to gain
by forcing him to eat?
‐ I want him to keep
eating more and more!
‐ Yes, but why?
‐ What do you mean, why?
I want him to eat lots and lots!
I want my dear customer
to have his fill.
Because having your fill of
every kind of delicious food
is pure happiness.
‐ I found you.
This person's heart is
not where you belong.
Let's go back.
‐ I'm not letting
him go anywhere!
Stay away!
‐ Miss Ebine!
What feeling is that shard?
‐ I just want him
to enjoy my cooking!
That's what a restaurant is for!
‐ Then why has your cooking
become so bland and cold?
(gasps)
Why would you force your
customer to eat such a meal?
Why would you lock him up?
I want you to tell me
what it is you're
feeling, Miss Ebine.
‐ What I'm feeling.
‐ Come dance with
me, Miss Ebine.
‐ Yes.
Back then, I felt a little
uncertainty, but mostly bliss.
I could have burst
with happiness.
The warm atmosphere,
happy conversations,
delicious food.
‐ [Tutu] What a
wonderful restaurant.
A wonderful couple.
‐ I'd set my dish next
to his and point, saying,
who will taste
better, you or you.
He'd tease me and point at mine.
You still have a long way to go.
But that was happiness for me.
Who will taste
better, you or you?
‐ [Tutu] That's what
those words meant.
‐ There's no one left to
tease me when I ask about it.
I have recipes, but the
person who cooked them
is no longer here.
I'm so lonely.
So I wanted to have my customers
stay as long as possible.
I could at least have that.
‐ You're the feeling of
loneliness, aren't you?
‐ The feeling of loneliness.
‐ Yes, but this is
not where you belong.
‐ I'm sorry, but I must go.
‐ Wait, don't go!
Please, I'll be alone again.
‐ Don't worry, you won't
be left alone, Miss Ebine.
Because you have the
recipes left behind
by the one you love, right here.
Lots of dishes are waiting,
wanting to be made.
A gift left to you by
the one who loved you.
The power to turn
loneliness into strength.
(weeping)
‐ My dear.
I feel like I can cook
warm dishes again.
Warm, just like your heart.
I'll make this a wonderful
restaurant again.
Please help me, my dear.
‐ My prince.
Your feelings belong
inside of you.
Your life belongs
within your heart.
‐ I'd like to thank
you, Princess Tutu.
‐ Oh Mytho.
(sighs)
All right.
‐ Mytho, what are
you doing here?
Hey!
‐ Well, nothing.
‐ So what happened, Mytho?
‐ Princess Tutu.
‐ [Duck] Don't tell
me he knows it's me!
‐ She appeared and touched me.
‐ Princess Tutu?
‐ This is ridiculous,
that's just a story.
‐ Huh? Tutu is part
of the story, too?
But I'm a duck!
‐ Though blessed with beauty,
cleverness and strength,
she's still a princess faded
never to be with her prince.
When she confesses her love,
she turns into a speck
of light and vanishes.
(screaming)
‐ What's part of the story?
What's real?
Tutu is me and I'm a duck,
but Tutu is, Tutu is...
‐ [Narrator] That's right,
Princess Tutu is
a tragic princess.
Stories aren't always
guaranteed a happily ever after.
(cackles)
(gentle music)
‐ [Duck] All I wanna do is find
the pieces of Mytho's heart
and give them back to him!
I'm not thinking
about being with him
or confessing to
him or anything.
‐ [Mytho] I don't know,
these emotions I'm feeling.
‐ [Fakir] You'd better
not be the one helping him
dredge up these weird things.
‐ [Rue] Maybe it was Princess
Tutu from the fairy tale.
‐ [Narrator] The story
will become real,
in this town where reality
and stories intermingle.
‐ I am Princess Tutu.
Just like you, I am
fated never to be
with the one whom I love.
‐ All who love stories,
gather 'round. (cackling)