-ONCE UPON A TIME,
THERE WAS A MAN WHO DIED.
THE STORY THE MAN WROTE
WAS ABOUT A HAPPY PRINCE
WHO LOVED EVERYONE
AND WAS LOVED BY EVERYONE.
THE PEOPLE FOUGHT, EACH WANTING
HIM TO LOVE THEM AND THEM ALONE,
AND AN EVIL RAVEN PECKED
AT THE LOVING HEARTS
OF ONE PERSON AFTER ANOTHER.
THE MORE THE PRINCE LOVED THEM
AND TRIED TO SAVE THEM,
THE MORE THE PEOPLE'S LOVE
JUST FED THE RAVEN.
IN THE END, THE RAVEN THOUGHT,
"I'D LIKE TO TRY
EATING THE PRINCE'S HEART,
THE MOST DELICIOUS ONE OF ALL."
[ RITSUKO OKAZAKI'S
"MORNING GRACE" PLAYS ]
-[ SINGING IN JAPANESE ]
-[ OWL HOOTING ]
-THANK YOU.
-HEY.
[ TWINKLE ]
-ALL RIGHT.
JUST WHAT'S GOING ON?
AND WHO IS SHE?
WHY DID THE STORY JUST --
-I WILL MAKE SURE
IT DOESN'T DOUBLE BACK AGAIN.
-FAKIR, WHAT ARE YOU
TRYING TO ACCOMPLISH?
WAIT A MINUTE!
YOU'RE NOT THINKING
OF REWRITING THE STORY
THAT'S CONTROLLING THIS TOWN,
ARE YOU?
-ALL I WANT IS THE POWER
TO PROTECT PEOPLE.
THAT'S IT.
AUTOR, CAN I ASK YOU SOMETHING?
-WHAT'S THAT?
-MY POWER --
IS IT REALLY SOMETHING
THAT MAKES STORIES INTO REALITY?
YOU'RE SURE
I'M NOT WRITING THINGS
THAT WILL BECOME REALITY ANYWAY?
-THE TWO ARE PART
OF THE SAME POWER.
LISTEN TO ME.
IF YOUR POWER IS IMMATURE,
THEN OF COURSE IT'S GOING TO BE
SWAYED BY REALITY.
BUT IF YOU DEVELOP
A STRONG POWER,
REALITY SHOULD START
BENDING TOWARDS
AND OBEYING YOUR STORIES.
IT WOULD THEN BE
A TRIVIAL MATTER TO MOVE ON
TO MANIPULATING THE FATES
OF ALL MANKIND.
-[ SIGHS ]
-[ Thinking ]
THE POWER TO PROTECT, EH?
DID I ACTUALLY
WRITE DOWN A STORY
THAT SAVED HER
WITH MY OWN POWER,
OR WAS I MADE TO WRITE IT?
HER FEELINGS FOR MYTHO
ARE SPILLING UP
THROUGH MY HANDS
AND OUT ONTO THE PAGE.
EVEN THOUGH
I COULDN'T WRITE ONE LETTER
OF A STORY ABOUT MYTHO,
I COULD WRITE A STORY
TO SAVE HER,
AS IF IT WERE FLOWING FROM ME.
BUT THE STORY I NEED TO WRITE
IS ABOUT MYTHO.
[ EXHALES SHARPLY ]
[ DOOR OPENS, CLOSES ]
-[ GROANS LIGHTLY ]
I'M AT FAKIR'S?
THAT MANUSCRIPT --
HE SAID HE WROTE THAT FOR ME.
[ DOOR OPENS ]
OH, UZURA!
I GUESS YOU GOT BACK SAFE,
TOO, HUH?
-[ EXHALES ]
-FAKIR!
-SO, YOU'RE AWAKE.
YOU'RE HUNGRY, RIGHT?
-YEAH.
[ GASPS ]
BUT THAT'S THE STORY YOU WROTE.
-IT'S A STORY THAT'S OVER NOW.
-[ Thinking ] THE STORY ABOUT ME
THAT FAKIR WROTE FOR ME.
I KIND OF WANTED TO READ IT,
BUT I'M REALLY GLAD YOU'RE ABLE
TO WRITE STORIES NOW, FAKIR.
[ SWALLOWS FOOD ]
AND THEN WHEN I TOLD HIM
THAT I THOUGHT THE FIVE GATES
HAD HEART SHARDS IN THEM,
HE SAID, "CONGRATULATIONS."
-SO, BASICALLY, THOSE SHARDS
ARE THE ONLY ONES
SEALING AWAY THE RAVEN.
-NOW WE CAN GO AND GET THEM ALL.
MM!
-WE COULD.
IT WOULD ALSO RESTORE THE RAVEN.
-HM? HM! [ CHOKES ]
[ COUGHS ]
-CALM DOWN, WILL YOU?
-HM! NHM!
-IT'S A BRIDGE
WE'LL HAVE TO CROSS EVENTUALLY.
AND IF WE DON'T GET MOVING,
MYTHO MIGHT NOT BE ABLE
TO RETURN TO NORMAL.
-YEAH, THAT'S TRUE!
I GUESS EVEN IF
THE RAVEN IS RESTORED,
IT'LL BE NO PROBLEM NOW
THAT YOU'VE GOT
THE POWER OF STORIES, RIGHT?
-YOU DO YOUR BEST.
-[ Thinking ] THAT'S RIGHT.
MYTHO HAS FAKIR,
AND HE HAS PRINCESS TUTU.
HE'LL NEVER LOSE TO THE RAVEN!
AND I'M SURE
RUE WILL RETURN TO NORMAL, TOO.
[ GASPS ]
[ BIRDS CHIRPING ]
[ GASPS ] RUE?
[ CROWS CAWING ]
-GOOD MORNING, PRINCE.
-PRINCE, HUH?
HUH.
HM?
-PRINCE, YOU'RE HUNGRY,
AREN'T YOU?
[ GASPS ]
[ MOUSE SQUEALING ]
-[ GASPS ]
[ SQUEALING CONTINUES ]
-HELLO, KRAEHE.
YES, I AM HUNGRY.
-[ GASPS ] STOP!
[ SQUEALING CONTINUES ]
[ PANTING ]
-NOW, WHAT DID YOU DO THAT FOR?
YOU LOVE ME, DON'T YOU?
YOU DON'T LOVE ME?
-MY LOVE HAS DONE NOTHING
BUT MAKE YOU INTO THIS.
[ Thinking ]
I HAVE NO RIGHT TO LOVE YOU.
[ WHIMPERS ]
-IS THAT...MYTHO?
-LET'S DANCE...MY PRINCE.
-OF COURSE.
-OH, PRINCE.
-I DON'T THINK I'VE EVER SEEN
RUE DANCE SO -- SO SADLY.
-DO YOU REMEMBER ALL THE
PAS DE DEUX WE DANCED TOGETHER?
YOU'RE MY PRINCE.
-THAT'S RIGHT.
-YEP. AFTER ALL,
THAT'S WHAT FATHER SAID.
-THE PRINCE WHO SEALED ME AWAY
DESERVES OUR HATRED.
[ GROWLS ]
BUT...HE IS THE ONE PRINCE
THAT YOU SHOULD MARRY, KRAEHE.
-HUH?
-A PRINCE WHO LOVES EVERYONE
SHOULD BE ABLE
TO SINCERELY LOVE EVEN
AN UGLY, PITIFUL GIRL LIKE YOU.
-YOU REALLY THINK?
-YES. I REALLY DO.
-[ Thinking ]
THE ONLY TIME I WAS HAPPY
WAS THE TIME
THAT I SPENT WITH YOU.
-MYTHO? MYTHO?
-[ Thinking ] I WANTED YOU
TO LOOK AT ME ALONE.
I WANTED
NEVER TO BE WITHOUT YOU,
NOT EVEN FOR A MOMENT.
SAY, LOOK, IS THIS PRETTY?
-YES.
I HAVE TO GET BACK
TO FAKIR'S SOON.
HE'LL BE GETTING WORRIED.
-WHAT? WAIT. WATCH ME!
-I'M SORRY.
-[ Voice breaking ]
NO! STAY AND WATCH ME, PLEASE!
I PRACTICED AS HARD AS I COULD!
[ Thinking ]
BUT YOU -- YOU DIDN'T.
-KRAEHE, GO TO THE HUMAN WORLD
AS A HUMAN GIRL
AND WIN THE PRINCE'S LOVE.
-YES, FATHER.
-AND IF YOU SHOULD EVER GET HOLD
OF A SHARD
OF THE PRINCE'S HEART,
I NEED YOU
TO BRING IT TO ME AT ONCE
BECAUSE I HAVE A TASK TO PERFORM
IN PREPARATION
FOR YOUR WEDDING TO HIM.
-I WILL.
-TODAY IS THE FIRST DAY
OF LESSONS
FOR THOSE
IN THE BEGINNERS' CLASS,
SO I'LL TAKE THIS TIME TO TALK
ABOUT BALLET AND MARRIAGE.
BALLET AND MARRIAGE
ARE INEXTRICABLY...
-HELLO, RUE.
-WE CAN SEE EACH OTHER
EVERY DAY NOW, MY PRINCE.
-MYTHO.
-HM?
-CALL MYTHO "PRINCE" AGAIN,
AND I'LL MAKE SURE
YOU REGRET IT.
-THEN I WON'T DO IT AS LONG AS
YOU AGREE NOT TO GET IN OUR WAY.
-[ SCOFFS ]
-I DIDN'T WANT ANYONE
TO KNOW I WAS A CROW,
SO I SEALED AWAY THEIR MEMORIES.
-MY BELOVED DAUGHTER...
-[ Voice breaking ]
I HONESTLY WAS CONVINCED
THAT I WAS FATHER'S DAUGHTER.
[ SOBBING ]
I'M A FOOL.
THERE'S NO WAY
A MERE HUMAN LIKE ME
COULD MARRY THE PRINCE
FROM THE STORY.
-SO ALL THIS TIME,
RUE REALLY WASN'T KRAEHE AT ALL.
-SHALL WE DANCE, KRAEHE?
-[ SOBBING ]
-[ GASPS ]
-[ CONTINUES SOBBING ]
-RUE?
-DUCK?
-WHY DOES MYTHO LOOK LIKE THAT?
-YOU SAW?
-UH, UNH...
-THAT'S RIGHT.
IT WAS MY FAULT.
-HUH?
-GO AHEAD.
LAUGH AT THE FOOLISH GIRL
TRICKED BY A RAVEN.
-I WOULDN'T LAUGH AT YOU.
-LIAR!
I KNOW YOU'RE THINKING
THIS SERVES ME RIGHT.
-NO, I'M NOT.
-LEAVE ME BE.
-RUE, INSIDE THE FIVE TOWN GATES
ARE THE HEART SHARDS
THAT ARE SEALING AWAY THE RAVEN.
IF WE RETURN THEM, I KNOW
MYTHO WILL GO BACK TO NORMAL.
-BUT THEY'RE
SEALING THE RAVEN AWAY?
N-NO! YOU MUSTN'T!
-WHAT?
-SHOULD THE RAVEN BE RESTORED
AND THE PRINCE GET HIS HEART
IN ITS ENTIRETY,
HE'LL GIVE HIS HEART
OVER TO THE RAVEN.
-WHAT?
BUT IF THE PRINCE
GOES BACK TO NORMAL --
-WHAT IF HE DOESN'T GO BACK
TO NORMAL?! WHAT THEN?!
-BUT I-I --
-THE RAVEN WAS USING US
TO MAKE THE PRINCE
GIVE HIM HIS HEART!
THAT'S ALL HE WANTED!
-NO, WAIT, BUT THEN --
-LISTEN TO ME!
DON'T DO ANYTHING ELSE!
-RUE, I --
-[ Crying ] I'M BEGGING YOU.
PLEASE STOP.
IF IT WERE ME,
IF I WERE PRINCESS TUTU,
I'D NEVER GIVE HIM
HIS HEART BACK.
-[ EXHALES SHARPLY ]
NOW WHAT?
WHAT SHOULD I DO?
-WHAT A SHAME FOR YOU,
LITTLE DUCK.
THE STORY WON'T END
THAT EASILY, YOU KNOW?
FIRST, THAT'S NOT NEARLY
TRAGIC ENOUGH.
[ CHUCKLES ]
[ BIRDS CHIRPING ]
-NOW WHAT?
QUACK!
[ TWINKLE ]
[ Weakly ] QUACK.
-WHAT'S WRONG WITH DUCK, ZURA?
-DUCK DOESN'T KNOW.
-HUH? THAT'S MYSELF
AS A PUPPET, ZURA.
-THERE'S A THING
SHE DOESN'T KNOW.
-A THING, ZURA?
-A TRUTH THAT SHOULD'VE BEEN
REVEALED
AFTER THE PRINCE'S HEART
WAS STOLEN BY THE RAVEN.
-THE PRINCE FROM "THE PRINCE
AND THE RAVEN" HAS BECOME REAL.
[ CUP AND SAUCER CLATTERING ]
I SEE.
AND THE RAVEN HAS BECOME REAL,
AS WELL,
AND IS BEING RESTORED
AS WE SPEAK!
THIS TOWN REALLY
IS BEING CONTROLLED BY STORIES.
MY HYPOTHESIS
WAS RIGHT ON THE MARK!
-I'M A KNIGHT WHO WAS GIVEN
THE FATE OF DEATH IN VAIN.
MY SWORD WOULD PROVE USELESS
IN PROTECTING THE PRINCE.
-SO YOU WANT TO WRITE?
-YES.
-WELL, TO BE FRANK,
YOU HAVE NO HOPE OF REWRITING
DROSSELMEYER'S STORIES
AT YOUR LEVEL OF POWER.
-[ SCOFFS ]
-IF YOU'RE ONLY WHERE THE STORY
IS WRITING ITSELF THROUGH YOU,
THEN THERE'S NO WAY YOU COULD
MAKE YOUR STORIES REALITY.
-I'M AWARE OF THAT!
THAT'S WHY I'M ASKING YOU
FOR YOUR HELP, AUTOR.
-AND JUST WHY SHOULD
I HAVE TO DO THAT FOR YOU?
-LISTEN, I NEED YOUR KNOWLEDGE.
-AND ALL I'M SAYING IS,
WHY SHOULD I?
-QUACK.
[ SIGHS ]
MYTHO -- WHAT DOES MYTHO
WANT ME TO DO?
[ SNARE DRUM TAPS ]
UNH? QUACK.
UZURA!
-YOU'RE GOING TO STOP
BEING DUCK, AREN'T YOU, ZURA?
-QUACK?
-MYSELF TOLD ME SO, ZURA.
-MYSELF?
QUA-QUA -- QUACK-QUACK-QUACK!
QUACK!
-MYSELF IS HERE INSIDE ME, ZURA.
-[ GRUNTS LIGHTLY ]
[ Thinking ]
THE SOUND OF UZURA'S HEART.
[ GEARS GRINDING,
WALTZ PLAYING ]
THIS MUSIC IS...
[GASPS] MISS EDEL!
-IT'S BEEN A WHILE,
HASN'T IT, DUCK?
-MISS EDEL!
-THERE'S A THING
THAT DUCK DOESN'T KNOW.
-WHAT?
-THE DUCK'S PENDANT.
-MY PENDANT?
-YES. THAT'S THE LAST
OF THE PRINCE'S HEART SHARDS.
-[ GASPS ]
-IT RESONATES
WITH THE HEART SHARDS
BECAUSE IT IS
A HEART SHARD ITSELF.
THAT SHARD IS WHAT AWAKENS
PRINCESS TUTU.
PRINCESS TUTU -- THE ONLY ONE
WHO CAN GIVE THE PRINCE'S HEART
BACK TO HIM.
-I GET IT.
BEFORE THE PRINCE
SHATTERED HIS HEART,
IT WAS HIS WILL
THAT HE'D SOMEDAY GET IT BACK.
ISN'T THAT RIGHT?
-HOWEVER, WHETHER OR NOT
THE DUCK RETURNS
THAT HEART SHARD TO THE PRINCE
DEPENDS ON HER OWN WILL.
-MISS EDEL.
[ Thinking ]
MY WILL IS THE SAME AS MYTHO'S.
QUACK.
-YOU LOOK LIKE
YOU FEEL BETTER, ZURA.
[ EXHALES ]
-QUACK!
[ TWINKLE ]
-THE PENDANT -- YOU'RE GIVING IT
TO THE PRINCE, ZURA?
-MM-HMM.
-AND THEN YOU'LL GO BACK
TO BEING A DUCK, ZURA?
-MM-HMM.
-[ Voice breaking ]
AND THEN WE WON'T BE ABLE
TO TALK TO EACH OTHER
ANYMORE, ZURA?
-MM-HMM.
[ TEARS TAPPING SNARE ]
-AND EVEN IF...
-[ GASPS ]
-...EVEN IF I PUT WATER ON YOU,
YOU WON'T CHANGE BACK, ZURA?
-YEAH, THAT'S RIGHT.
THAT ME IS THE REAL ME.
-YOU'RE REALLY A DUCK, ZURA?
-MM-HMM.
NOW, DON'T CRY, OKAY?
-OKAY, ZURA.
-UZURA! NO!
THAT CURSED EDEL HAD TO BUTT IN.
THAT WAS THE SECRET I WAS SAVING
FOR MY LAST BIT OF FUN.
WELL, NO MATTER,
WITH THINGS AS THEY ARE,
THEY WON'T BE ABLE
TO ESCAPE THE TRAGEDY.
-AAAH!
AAH-AH!
AH-AH!
[ GRUNTING ]
AAAH!
-[ PANTING, GASPS ]
-[ BREATHING HEAVILY ]
-[ WHIMPERS LIGHTLY ]
-MYTHO.
[ WHIMPERS LIGHTLY ]
-WON'T YOU DANCE WITH ME?
WHY ARE YOU SO...
SO FRIGHTENED OF ME?!
AAAAAH!
-[ GASPS ]
HE'S RIGHT.
JUST NOW,
I WAS...AFRAID OF MYTHO.
-WHOA! SCARY!
-OH!
-AAH!
-[ PANTING ]
[ CROWS CAWING ]
-[ WHIMPERS ]
[ GASPS ]
THE PRINCE!
[ WHOOSH ]
-[ GRUNTS ]
KRAEHE, DANCE WITH ME.
-[ WHIMPERS LIGHTLY ]
-[ GROANS ]
WHEN I'M NOT DANCING
WITH SOMEONE,
I'M UNEASY AND LONELY.
AND IT HURTS SO MUCH,
I CAN'T STAND IT.
-MY PRINCE.
I'M SORRY, MY PRINCE.
YOU'RE SUFFERING
BECAUSE OF THE RAVEN'S BLOOD.
THE HEARTS OF THESE BIRDS
HURT PEOPLE.
-OH.
-EVEN THE PEOPLE YOU LOVE.
THE MORE LOVE YOU HAVE FOR THEM,
THE MORE PAIN YOU CAUSE THEM.
WITH MY OWN HANDS,
I'VE THROWN INTO CHAOS
THIS HEART OF YOURS
THAT LOVES EVERYONE.
[ Voice breaking ] EVERY PART
OF THIS HAS BEEN MY FAULT,
JUST BECAUSE I WANTED TO HAVE
YOUR LOVE ALL TO MYSELF.
I'M SO SORRY.
-RUE.
-[ GASPS ] TUTU.
-THIS PENDANT THAT TRANSFORMS ME
INTO PRINCESS TUTU
IS ALSO A SHARD
FROM THE PRINCE'S HEART,
SO IT IS THE WILL
OF THE PRINCE HIMSELF
TO HAVE ALL OF HIS HEART
RETURNED TO HIM.
I'LL ACT ACCORDING
TO THE PRINCE'S WILL.
LET'S BOTH BELIEVE
IN THE PRINCE.
-ALL RIGHT, THEN.
-[ Thinking ] SHARDS, ENTER ME.
HERE I AM!
[ HIGH-PITCHED WHIRRING ]
[ DOORS CREAK ]
[ WHIRRING RESUMES ]
[ RUMBLING ]
-LOOK AT WHAT YOU'VE BECOME.
-SO, THIS IS THE PRINCE?
HOW LAMENTABLE.
-WHAT?
-DOESN'T IT SEEM
LIKE IT'S ALREADY TOO LATE?
-WHAT CAN WE DO BUT RETURN
TO OUR ORIGINAL HEART?
-LET'S PREPARE OURSELVES.
THE RAVEN IS ABOUT TO REVIVE.
LET US NOT WAVER.
[ TWINKLING ]
-[ GASPS ]
-PRINCESS TUTU, THANK YOU.
HOWEVER, IF EVEN AFTER
I GO BACK INSIDE MY HEART
AND THE RAVEN'S CURSE
HAS NOT BEEN LIFTED...
-WHAT?
-...I ASK YOU, YOU PLEASE NOT
RETURN THE FINAL HEART SHARD.
-BUT I...
-IF THAT HAPPENS, PLEASE FIND
A WAY TO LIFT THE CURSE QUICKLY.
-BUT THAT'S --
-WE DON'T HAVE
A MOMENT TO SPARE NOW.
[ TWINKLE ]
-[ GASPS ]
IF THAT IS WHAT
THE PRINCE WILLS.
[ GRUNTS LIGHTLY ]
[ TWINKLING ]
-[ GASPS ]
[ GROANING ]
-MY PRINCE!
-[ GASPS ]
[ RUMBLING, THUNDER BOOMING ]
-[ GROANING ]
-[ GASPS ]
-PRINCE...WE FINALLY MEET AGAIN.
-SO THIS IS THE RAVEN.
-NOW, KRAEHE,
BRING THE PRINCE HERE.
-[ WHIMPERS LIGHTLY ]
NO!
-WHAT?
THEN YOU DON'T MIND
LOSING MY LOVE?
-MY FATHER IS NO RAVEN!
AND AS FOR YOU, YOU'RE A LIAR!
-HMM. [ CHUCKLES ]
YOU FOUND OUT.
I RAISED YOU
DRINKING MY NOBLE BLOOD
EVER SINCE YOU WERE A BABY.
BUT IN THE END, YOU'RE NOTHING
MORE THAN A FOOLISH HUMAN GIRL.
IT'S BAD ENOUGH YOU COULDN'T
TURN THE PRINCE'S AFFECTIONS
TOWARDS YOU
LIKE YOUR BLOOD DEMANDED,
BUT TO THINK
YOU SUCCUMBED TO LOVE.
-I HAVE
NO NEED OF RAVEN'S BLOOD!
WHEN I WAS RUE, I WAS RUE.
THAT WAS WHEN I WAS HAPPIEST.
-OH, RUE.
-WHAT A WASTE OF MY TIME.
NOW, PRINCE,
COME TO ME ON YOUR OWN POWER.
GIVE ME YOUR HEART.
-YOU MUSTN'T'!
-[ CAWING ]
-[ GASPS ] YOU MUSTN'T GO!
-[ GASPS ]
-NO! PLEASE DON'T GO!
-[ CAWING ]
-DON'T GO!
PRINCE!
-PRINCE, PLEASE WAIT.
-[ CAWS ] CAW!
-AAAH! AAH!
-[ LAUGHING EVILLY ]
-NO! LET THE PRINCE GO!
DON'T EAT THE PRINCE'S HEART!
[ WHIMPERS ] LET HIM GO
AND EAT MY HEART INSTEAD!
PLEASE! I LOVE YOU! MY PRINCE!
I HAVE EVER SINCE I WAS LITTLE!
I'VE ALWAYS LOVED YOU!
[ WARBLING ]
-[ GASPS ]
-WHAT IS THIS FEELING I HAVE?
-YOU DARE INTERFERE?
-[ GRUNTS ]
-THIS FRAIL, EARNEST LOVE.
I MUST...
-[ EXHALES SHARPLY ]
-...I MUST PROTECT THIS LOVE.
TUTU.
TUTU, WERE YOU THE ONE
WHO HELPED ME?
-MNH-MNH. [ GASPS ]
-[ LAUGHS EVILLY ]
FOR YOU TO LOVE HIM SO MUCH,
YOU'D GIVE UP YOUR LIFE.
YOU'RE A FOOLISH GIRL
TO THE END.
[ CROWS CAWING ]
[ RITSUKO OKAZAKI'S "ALTHOUGH
MY LOVE IS SMALL" PLAYS ]
-[ SINGING IN JAPANESE ]
-WHEN THAT HAPPENS, I'LL GO BACK
TO BEING JUST A BIRD,
AND I WON'T EVER STUDY BALLET
WITH EVERYBODY AGAIN.
-THAT'S FINE, ISN'T IT?
AFTER ALL,
THAT'S WHO YOU REALLY ARE.
-I WOULD LIKE FOR YOU
TO RETURN MY FINAL HEART SHARD.
-SAY, UH,
I HAVE ANOTHER QUESTION.
DO YOU THINK HE'LL LOVE ME?
-LET'S GO BACK
TO BEING OUR TRUE SELVES NOW.
-GOODBYE, NOW, MYTHO.
GOODBYE.
-ALL YOU CHILDREN
WHO LOVE STORIES,
COME GATHER 'ROUND.
[ LAUGHS EVILLY ]