-ONCE UPON A TIME,
MANY YEARS AGO,
THERE WAS A HAPPY PRINCE.
HE RECALLED NO PAINFUL PAST
AND KNEW NO PAINFUL FUTURE.
ONE DAY, THE PRINCE
OBTAINED A COMFORTING WARMTH.
THE SOURCE OF THIS WARMTH,
HOWEVER,
EMANATED NOT ONLY TRANQUILITY
BUT ALSO UNHAPPINESS, PAIN,
AND LONELINESS.
[ RITSUKO OKAZAKI'S
"MORNING GRACE" PLAYS ]
-[ SINGING IN JAPANESE ]
[ SINGING CONTINUES ]
[ TCHAIKOVSKY'S "FINAL
WALTZ AND APOTHEOSIS" FROM
"THE NUTCRACKER" PLAYS ]
[ BIRDS CHIRPING ]
[ SLOW FOOTSTEPS APPROACH ]
-WHAT ARE YOU READING?
-NOTHING.
IT'S NONE OF YOUR BUSINESS.
-"THE PRINCE AND THE RAVEN,"
HUH?
I SEE.
-WHAT?
-SEEMS
YOU'VE GAINED AN INTEREST
IN SEEING MYTHO
AS HE WAS IN THE STORY,
BACK BEFORE HE LOST HIS HEART.
-ARE YOU IMPLYING I'M THE ONE
RESTORING MYTHO'S HEART?
-AM I WRONG, THEN?
HOLD IT.
-[ GASPS ]
[ CHUCKLES ]
-WHAT'S SO FUNNY?
-WHAT WOULD YOU DO
IF PRINCESS TUTU REALLY EXISTED?
-DID SOMETHING HAPPEN?
-NO, NOTHING HAPPENED.
[ CHUCKLES ]
[ MID-TEMPO PIANO MUSIC PLAYS ]
-YES, THAT'S RIGHT.
ELONGATE YOUR SPINE.
-HEY, DUCK,
MADE UP YOUR MIND YET?
-ABOUT WHAT?
[ BOTH GASP ]
WHAT?
-DID YOU FORGET
WHAT'S GOING ON TODAY?
-UM, I GUESS I DID.
-[ GASPS ]
-HUH?
-THE FIRE FESTIVAL.
-THE WHAT, NOW?
-DON'T YOU REMEMBER?
WE'RE ASKING IF YOU'VE
DECIDED WHAT YOU'RE GONNA
WEAR TO THE FESTIVAL.
-SO, WHAT'S
THIS FIRE FESTIVAL AGAIN?
-OH, IT'S OKAY, DUCK! IT'S OKAY!
EVEN IF YOU LACK ANY COMMON
SENSE LIVING IN THIS TOWN
AND NOT KNOWING ABOUT
THE FIRE FESTIVAL,
YOU'RE JUST SO DARN CUTE!
-[ Thinking ] BECAUSE
I'M JUST A BIRD TO BEGIN WITH.
-MISS DUCK.
-YEAH, YEAH. SO, I'M A DUCK.
-MISS DUCK!
-I KNOW, ALREADY!
-I GET IT!
TELL ME ABOUT THE FIRE FESTIVAL!
OOH!
-VERY WELL.
I'LL TELL YOU.
-Y-YES, SIR.
-THE FIRE FESTIVAL
IS A TOWN FêTE
WHERE FOLKS DRESS IN
THE OLD WAYS AND DANCE
'ROUND A BONFIRE.
-I SEE, THEN.
I THINK I UNDERSTAND IT NOW.
-BUT MOST IMPORTANT OF ALL
IS THE GOLDEN APPLE
GIVEN TO THE COUPLE
WHO DANCES THE MOST EXQUISITELY
AT THE EVENT.
-GOLDEN APPLE?
-THAT'S RIGHT.
IT'S SAID THAT THE COUPLE TO
WHOM THE GOLDEN APPLE IS GIVEN
WILL BE BOUND TOGETHER FOREVER.
-BOUND TOGETHER FOREVER?
BUT THAT'S
NOTHING TO DO WITH ME.
-MISS DUCK.
-RIGHT, BECAUSE I'M A DUCK.
-MISS DUCK!
-BUT THAT'S OKAY. I KNOW IT!
-MISS DUCK!!
-I SAID I KNOW THA--
OH.
I'M SO SORRY.
-[ YOWLS, HISSES ]
AS PUNISHMENT
FOR YOUR LACK OF FOCUS,
YOU WILL CLEAN THE
ADVANCED CLASS'S LESSON ROOM.
IF YOU DON'T DO IT PROPERLY...
I WILL HAVE YOU MARRY ME!
[ YOWLING ]
-[ WHINES ]
-BE A GOOD GIRL
AND CLEAN THE ROOM.
-YES, 'CAUSE IF YOU
WIN THE APPLE BY SOME FLUKE,
YOU'LL BE BOUND.
-MYTHO.
MYTHO.
I TOLD HIM NOT TO LEAVE
WITHOUT ASKING.
-[ SIGHS ]
THE GOLDEN APPLE, HUH?
-TRY NOT TO FORGET, NOW.
THE PRINCESS
WHO SAVES THE PRINCE
IS FATED NEVER
TO BE WITH HER DEARLY BELOVED.
-[ GRUMBLES ] I DON'T CARE.
HMM?
[ GASPS ] OH!
AAH!
MYTHO?
HE'S A PRINCE.
IS THIS THE REAL YOU, MYTHO?
-TRY NOT TO FORGET, NOW --
SOON AS YOU CONFESS YOUR LOVE,
YOU'LL TURN INTO
A SPECK OF LIGHT AND VANISH.
-UH, UH, THAT IS,
I'M ON CLEANING DUTY
AS PUNISHMENT,
SO, PLEASE, DON'T MIND ME.
-HAVE YOU SEEN RUE ANYWHERE?
-HUH?
UH...
SEEN RUE?
-RUE SAID SHE WANTED TO PRACTICE
DANCING FOR THE FIRE FESTIVAL,
SO I'VE BEEN
WAITING HERE ALL DAY.
-OH.
SO MYTHO'S GOING TO BE
DANCING WITH RUE TONIGHT.
OF COURSE.
-WHEN I'M ALONE...
-[ GASPS ]
-...IT FEELS SO DARK AND COLD.
-FEELINGS?
-WILL YOU BE GOING TONIGHT,
DUCK?
-OH...
HE JUST CALLED ME BY NAME.
[ GASPS ]
AHHH.
[ TWINKLE! TWINKLE! ]
-COME, DUCK. LET'S DANCE.
-[ GASPS ] MYTHO! AAH!
I CAN'T GO TO THE FIRE FESTIVAL.
HUH?!
MYTHO WANTED --
MYTHO WANTED TO DANCE
OF HIS OWN WILL!
COULD IT BE BECAUSE
HE'S REGAINING HIS HEART?
IF IT IS, I'D BE HAPPY.
[ MID-TEMPO
CLASSICAL MUSIC PLAYS ]
-UH...
[ STAMMERS ]
-HER AGAIN.
DAMN.
-[ GASPS ] PLEASE, EXCUSE ME.
UNH.
[ CHUCKLES ]
I CAN'T BELIEVE IT!
I DANCED WITH MYTHO THE PRINCE!
[ LAUGHS ]
-HAVE YOU SEEN RUE ANYWHERE?
-BUT THAT WAS IN RUE'S PLACE.
[ SIGHS ]
-HUH?
-[ GROANING ]
-SHE PRACTICALLY IS A DUCK.
-CLEANING! OH!
-HEY!
[ GROANS ]
-[ GRUNTS ]
THAT VOICE JUST NOW.
OHH.
[ DOOR OPENS ]
I KNEW IT WAS HIM.
[ DOOR CLOSES ]
UH...
QUACK, QUACK, QUACK,
QUACK, QUACK, QUACK.
-[ Muffled ]
WHAT'S THE MEANING OF THIS?
-QUACK?! QUACK?
-DRESSED IN THIS SILLY OUTFIT.
-RUE SAID TO WEAR IT.
-LISTEN, ALL YOU HAVE TO DO
IS OBEY MY ORDERS
AND DON'T PAY ANY HEED
TO WHAT ANYONE ELSE TELLS YOU.
THAT INCLUDES WHAT RUE SAYS.
SO, YOU WERE DANCING?
-YES.
-WHAT'S WITH THAT DUCKLIKE GIRL
THAT I'VE SEEN
SCURRYING AROUND LATELY?
-DUCKLIKE?
WELL, I AM A DUCK, BUT --
-SHE'S CALLED "DUCK."
HER NAME IS DUCK.
-I DIDN'T ASK FOR TRIVIA.
-QUACK.
-THERE'S NO NEED TO DANCE
WITH THE LIKES OF HER
JUST BECAUSE SHE ASKED.
-THAT'S NOT WHAT HAPPENED.
RUE HADN'T COME,
AND I'D BEEN WAITING BY MYSELF.
THEN DUCK CAME, SO...
-ARE YOU SAYING
YOU INVITED HER TO DANCE?
-YES.
-DON'T MAKE ME REPEAT MYSELF.
ALL YOU HAVE TO DO
IS LISTEN TO WHAT I TELL YOU
AND STOP WASTING YOUR TIME
ON SUCH USELESS NONSENSE.
-[ GRUNTS ] I CAN'T HEAR.
-WHEN YOU WERE
WANDERING AIMLESSLY,
COMPLETELY STRIPPED
OF ALL YOUR MEMORIES,
I WAS THE ONE
WHO GAVE YOU THE NAME OF MYTHO.
I'M THE ONE WHO SAVED YOU,
AND DON'T EVER FORGET THAT.
-HMM.
-YOU WILL STAY HOME. GOT IT?
BEING AS YOU ARE NOW
IS FOR THE BEST.
-BUT RUE...
WANTS ME TO DANCE WITH HER.
-FORGET ABOUT RUE.
-I HAVE TO LET HER KNOW
I CAN'T GO.
-ARE YOU DEFYING ME?
-NO, BUT --
-COME WITH ME.
-OH.
QUACK, QUACK, QUACK, QUACK,
QUACK, QUACK, QUACK!
-WHERE ARE WE GOING, FAKIR?
FAKIR?
-NEVER MIND THAT.
-QUACK, QUACK, QUACK,
QUACK, QUACK, QUACK, QUACK.
QUACK?
THE LIBRARY? QUACK!
QUACK, QUACK, QUACK, QUACK,
QUACK, QUACK, QUACK -- AAH!
WOW!
RUE!
BUT FAKIR TOOK MYTHO AWAY.
OH, ANYWAY, I HAVE TO
GO BACK TO BEING DUCK THE GIRL.
WATER. WATER! QUACK!
[ DING! ]
OHHHH.
[ TWINKLE! ]
[ GRUNTS ] YES!
RUE!
-DUCK.
-S-SO, UH, YOU'RE
MEETING UP WITH MYTHO, RIGHT?
-[ CHUCKLES ]
HOW DO YOU KNOW THAT?
-UH, WELL, UH, Y-YOU SEE,
THE TRUTH IS I WAS KIND OF PUT
ON CLEANING DUTY AS PUNISHMENT,
SO I WAS IN HERE CLEANING
NOT TOO LONG AGO,
AND MYTHO WAS HERE, TOO,
AND HE SAID
HE WAS GONNA PRACTICE
DANCING WITH YOU.
WOW. IT'S TOTALLY WET OVER HERE.
OF COURSE, I'M THE ONE
WHO MADE THE MESS. [ LAUGHS ]
-SO, WHERE'S MYTHO?
-OH. I THINK
HE STEPPED OUT FOR A BIT.
-HMM. WHAT,
YOU DIDN'T GO CHASE HIM DOWN
LIKE YOU DID THE OTHER DAY?
-OH. WELL...
-AND THEN YOU SUDDENLY
DISAPPEARED FOR SOME REASON.
-[ CHUCKLES NERVOUSLY ]
YEAH. SORRY.
-IF YOU HAPPEN TO SEE MYTHO,
PLEASE TELL HIM I'LL BE
GOING ON AHEAD TO THE SQUARE.
-OH. OKAY.
HEY, RUE.
MYTHO WILL COME AND FIND YOU.
I'M SURE HE WILL.
YOU'RE LIKE A REAL PRINCESS,
AND YOU REALLY SUIT EACH OTHER,
SO I'M SURE YOU'LL
GET THE GOLDEN APPLE, TOO.
[ INDISTINCT CONVERSATIONS ]
[ TCHAIKOVSKY'S "MARCH"
FROM "THE NUTCRACKER" PLAYS ]
-I KNOW THEY
WENT IN THE LIBRARY FOR SURE,
BUT, MM...
-STAY THERE AND BEHAVE YOURSELF.
-WHY?
-PUNISHMENT.
-I'M SORRY. DON'T BE MAD, FAKIR.
I'LL DO AS YOU SAY.
FAKIR, I --
-WHAT ARE YOU DOING?!
PUNISHMENT?!
WHY DO YOU ALWAYS
DO SUCH TERRIBLE THINGS?!
AND YOU, MYTHO --
RUE'S WAITING FOR YOU!
YOU FINALLY HAVE SOME SHARDS
OF YOUR HEART BACK NOW!
YOU DON'T HAVE TO LISTEN
TO HIM ANYMO-- [ GASPS ]
-SHARDS OF HIS HEART?
YOUR NAME'S DUCK, RIGHT?
JUST WHAT DO YOU KNOW?
-N-NOTHING, REALLY.
-COME TO THINK OF IT,
YOU ASKED ME ABOUT
"THE PRINCE AND THE RAVEN"
THAT ONE TIME.
-[ GASPS ]
-YOU KNOW, DON'T YOU?
YOU KNOW THAT MYTHO IS ACTUALLY
A PRINCE FROM INSIDE A STORY.
-[ GASPS ]
-DID RUE TELL YOU?
-RUE?
RUE AND THIS PERSON
BOTH KNOW MYTHO'S SECRET?
AAH! UGH! UGH!
-MYTHO HAS NO NEED OF A HEART.
-HUH? HAS NO NEED OF A HEART?
WHAT ARE YOU SAYING?
THERE'S NO WAY.
-AND JUST WHAT DO YOU KNOW?
I KNOW EVERYTHING ABOUT MYTHO.
WHAT DO YOU KNOW?
-WELL, SURE, I MAY NOT
KNOW ANYTHING ABOUT MYTHO,
BUT IF HE'S MISSING HIS HEART,
HE WON'T KNOW HOW IT FEELS
TO BE HAPPY OR BE IN LOVE,
EITHER.
THAT'S WHY --
-FORGET IT.
EVEN IF HE REGAINS
SHARDS OF HIS HEART,
I'LL SEAL HIM AWAY.
IF I SHUT HIM AWAY
IN THE DARKNESS,
HE'LL BECOME NUMB
EVEN TO THE DARK.
NUMB TO ALL SENSATION,
HE'LL STOP FEELING ALL TOGETHER.
-THAT'S JUST --
THAT'S JUST TERRIBLE OF YOU!
[ CRYING ]
-DON'T LET YOUR IGNORANCE
CARRY YOU AWAY.
-ACTING SO HIGH AND MIGHTY,
LIKE HE KNOWS EVERYTHING.
WHEN I GAVE MYTHO BACK HIS
HEART SHARDS, HE THANKED ME.
HE DID!
-[ LAUGHS ]
ARE YOU AFRAID OF THE DARK?
YOU'LL BE OKAY.
-BUT IT'S TRUE.
I DON'T KNOW ANYTHING --
NOT WHEN IT COMES TO MYTHO.
AM I STICKING MY NOSE
WHERE IT DOESN'T BELONG?
[ UP-TEMPO MUSIC PLAYING ]
MISS EDEL!
-THE FLAME CAN ILLUMINATE
THE DARKNESS,
BUT WITHOUT THE DARKNESS,
ITS GLOW CANNOT BE SEEN.
ARE YOU AFRAID OF THE DARK?
-[ GASPS ]
-I SEE YOU'RE
IN THE DARKNESS OF UNCERTAINTY.
BUT IF YOU WISH TO SHINE
FOR SOMEONE,
YOU MUST NOT FEAR THE DARKNESS.
-I SEE.
YOU MEAN I SHOULDN'T FEAR
WHAT I DON'T UNDERSTAND, RIGHT?
-HMM.
A PATH IS OPEN TO YOU.
-WHAT? HE'S NOT HERE?
MYTHO, WHERE DID YOU GO?!
QUACK, QUACK, QUACK, QUACK,
QUACK!
AAAAAAAAAAAAH!
OHH! QUACK!
QUACK, QUACK, QUACK!
[ GRUNTS ]
QUACK! QUACK!
AAH!
[ DRIP! TWINKLE! ]
[ TWINKLE! ]
[ GASPS ]
OHH.
HUH?
THIS IS WHAT IT LOOKS LIKE
UNDER THE LIBRARY?
-[ LAUGHING ]
-[ GASPS ]
OH, IT'S A HEART SHARD.
-[ LAUGHING CONTINUES ]
-WHO'S THERE? MYTHO?
ARE YOU THERE?
-I'M JUST A LITTLE THING,
BUT I FLOOD THE ENTIRE ROOM.
-WHAT AM I?
-A RIDDLE?
HMM?
-[ LAUGHING ]
-[ GASPS ]
-[ LAUGHING CONTINUES ]
-IT'S COMING
FROM THE OTHER SIDE.
I MUSTN'T FEAR THE DARKNESS.
OKAY, JUST A LITTLE THING
THAT FLOODS THE ENTIRE ROOM.
OH, A SNEEZE!
-TOO BAD.
I'M A WHITE SNAKE
THAT SWALLOWS THE SEA.
WHAT AM I?
-UM, A WHITE PAINTBRUSH
WITH RED PAINT ON IT?
-[ LAUGHS ] TOO BAD.
HERE'S THE LAST ONE.
I BECOME SHORTER
THE LONGER I STAND. WHAT AM I?
-SO, YOU'RE, LIKE,
A FLOWER, RIGHT?
-TOO BAD.
BUT CONGRATULATIONS.
THE PERSON YOU'RE LOOKING FOR
IS HERE.
-WHAT? MYTHO?
GIVE HIM BACK!
-NO.
-AAH!
-YOU ALSO ARE TO STAY HERE.
-I CAN'T DO THAT!
-YOU'LL BE FINE. I'M HERE.
-WHO...ARE YOU?
-OH, DEAR. OH, DEAR.
ARE YOU TO BECOME A PRISONER OF
THE DARKNESS, NOW AND FOREVER,
OR WILL YOU BE ABLE TO REKINDLE
YOUR RADIANCE, PRINCESS TUTU?
[ TWINKLE! ]
-ARE YOU THERE?
-WHO ARE YOU?
-I AM PRINCESS TUTU.
-YOU'RE WONDERFUL.
PLEASE STAY AND DANCE.
I'LL ILLUMINATE YOU
FOR THE REST OF YOUR LIFE.
-ILLUMINATE ME?
-THAT'S RIGHT.
-SO, THAT'S IT --
THE LITTLE THING THAT FLOODS
THE ENTIRE ROOM
IS THE LIGHT OF A LAMP, THEN.
AND THE WHITE SNAKE WITH THE RED
HEAD THAT SWALLOWS THE SEA
AND BECOMES SHORTER THE LONGER
IT STANDS IS THE LAMP'S WICK.
YOU'RE A LAMP.
AM I RIGHT?
-YOU ARE CORRECT.
-HMM.
NOW, PLEASE, GIVE BACK MYTHO
AND HIS HEART.
-NO.
[ INDISTINCT CONVERSATIONS ]
-IDIOT.
-PLEASE DANCE WITH ME.
-DANCE WITH YOU?
-YES.
[ GASPS ]
-YOU DANCE.
I WILL LIGHT YOUR STEPS.
-MM.
[ TWINKLE! TWINKLE! TWINKLE! ]
YOUR LIGHT
IS SO WARM AND GENTLE.
WHY ARE YOU DOING THIS?
WHAT DO YOU WANT?
-MY ONE WISH -- MY ONLY WISH --
IS TO KEEP ON SHINING
FOR SOMEONE.
I WANT TO ENVELOP THEM TENDERLY
IN WARM LIGHT.
-WANTING TO SHINE FOR SOMEONE?
-THAT WAS ALL.
I DIDN'T WANT ANYTHING ELSE.
AND YET SOMEWHERE ALONG THE WAY,
I HAD SUDDENLY BECOME FORGOTTEN.
THE PEOPLE
WHO ARE PRECIOUS TO ME
FORGOT ABOUT ME
AND THE LIGHT I GAVE THEM.
NO, THEY MUST NOT HAVE NEEDED ME
FROM THE BEGINNING.
-THAT CAN'T BE TRUE.
-I THOUGHT
THEY ENJOYED MY PRESENCE,
BUT THAT WAS ONLY
WHEN I BELIEVED.
-I'M SURE THAT'S NOT TRUE.
-BUT RIGHT NOW, THERE IS SOMEONE
WHO WANTS MY LIGHT.
-[ GASPS ] MYTHO.
IS THAT WHAT YOU WANT --
TO SHUT HIM AWAY?
-YES.
I WILL STAY HERE
AND ILLUMINATE HIM FOR ALL TIME.
-PLEASE,
REMEMBER WHAT IT WAS LIKE
TO HAVE YOUR WARM LIGHT SHINE
ON THE PEOPLE YOU LOVE.
-I HAVEN'T FORGOTTEN.
-THEN YOU SHOULD KNOW
FORCING YOUR WARMTH ON PEOPLE
WON'T BRING JOY TO ANYONE.
I LOVE THE SOFT AND TENDER GLOW
OF YOUR WARM LIGHT.
I BELIEVE THAT THE PEOPLE
WHO ARE PRECIOUS TO YOU
WERE VERY HAPPY TO HAVE YOU
ENVELOP THEM WITH THAT GLOW.
IT'S SAD
THAT THEY NO LONGER NEED YOU,
BUT IT'S SOMETHING
THAT CAN'T BE HELPED,
BECAUSE IT ISN'T SOMETHING
THAT YOU CAN FORCE ON PEOPLE.
IF YOU WANT WHAT IS BEST
FOR MYTHO,
RETURN HIS HEART.
THAT WILL BRING HIM HAPPINESS.
-WILL IT?
-IT'S WHAT I BELIEVE.
-PRINCESS TUTU, I WANT TO
CONTINUE ILLUMINATING YOU.
-I AM THE FEELING OF AFFECTION
SHATTERED AND FORGOTTEN.
-THE FEELING OF AFFECTION.
[ TWINKLE! TWINKLE! ]
-OH.
RETURN TO MYTHO NOW.
[ TWINKLE! ]
-[ GRUNTS SOFTLY ]
-[ GASPS ]
MYTHO.
-PRINCESS TUTU.
-YOU SHOULD HURRY NOW.
-HUH?
-SOMEONE IS WAITING FOR YOU.
[ INDISTINCT CONVERSATIONS ]
-HMPH.
I WAS SUCH A FOOL
FOR BELIEVING WHAT DUCK SAID.
[ GASPS ]
MYTHO.
THE FIRE FESTIVAL ENDED
LONG AGO.
-SORRY.
-MYTHO, WHAT ARE YOU DOING?
MYTHO?
[ SAINT-SAENS' "AQUARIUM"
FROM "CARNIVAL OF
THE ANIMALS" PLAYS ]
STOP IT.
YOU'RE ACTING STRANGE.
-THIS IS HOW IT SHOULD BE.
-[ LAUGHS ]
[ MUSIC CONTINUES ]
[ GASPS ]
FOR SUCH KINDNESS TO BE
IN YOUR EYES, IT'S...
-RUE.
-[ GASPS ]
[ MUSIC CONTINUES ]
OH, RUE.
-THE PRINCE REGAINED
THE FEELING OF HAPPINESS,
BUT HAS IT ILLUMINATED
DUCK'S UNHAPPINESS?
[ LAUGHS EVILLY ]
[ SLOW MUSIC PLAYING ]
-[ SINGING IN JAPANESE ]
-LOVE?!
IT'S REALLY NOT ANYTHING
LIKE THAT WITH ME!
-I'M SURE.
SHE'S PURSUING
A WONDERFUL DREAM,
AND CHANCES ARE
SHE'S ALSO IN LOVE.
-YOU'LL ALWAYS WAKE UP
FROM A DREAM.
-NO.
-YOU MUST WAKE UP.
-WHAT'S THIS?
YOU'RE TREMBLING.
-I'M AFRAID OF PRINCESS TUTU.
-I JUST WANTED MYTHO TO SMILE.
THAT'S ALL I WANTED.
HAVE I JUST DONE
SOMETHING TERRIBLE TO MYTHO?
-ALL WHO LOVE STORIES,
GATHER 'ROUND.
[ LAUGHS EVILLY ]