-ONCE UPON A TIME,
THERE WAS A YOUNG WOMAN.
THE YOUNG WOMAN WAS TO MARRY
A GROOM CHOSEN BY HER PARENTS,
AND NOT HER SWEETHEART,
WHOM SHE LOVED.
SHE KNEW THAT HER GROOM
LOVED HER VERY MUCH,
BUT DID HER SWEETHEART CARE
FOR HER EVEN MORE THAN THAT?
THE YOUNG WOMAN WASN'T CERTAIN.
IN THE END, AFTER WAVERING
BETWEEN THE TWO OF THEM,
THE YOUNG WOMAN
EVEN BECAME UNSURE
WHICH ONE OF THEM
SHE REALLY LOVED.
[ RITSUKO OKAZAKI'S
"MORNING GRACE" PLAYS ]
-[ SINGING IN JAPANESE ]
[ SINGING CONTINUES ]
-HOW LONG HAVE I BEEN SEARCHING
FOR A WAY TO RETURN MYTHO
TO THE STORY?
ALL THIS TIME, I JUST TOOK
TO HAND WHATEVER BOOK STRUCK ME.
[ CLOCK TICKING ]
SO WHY DO I CHOOSE ONLY BOOKS
WHOSE ENDINGS ARE MISSING?
WHY?
WHAT MEANING IS THERE TO BOOKS
WITH MISSING ENDINGS?
I --
-[ LAUGHS ]
FOUND YOU.
-HUH?
-GEEZ, DUCK!
CAN'T YOU GO ONE DAY
WITHOUT GETTING STUCK
WITH CLEANING DUTY?
-OF COURSE SHE CAN'T!
-SORRY.
-SERIOUSLY, DUCK.
AAH!
-NO WAY!
-HUH? WHAT?!
-NO, DUCK, YOU MUSTN'T LOOK!
-AAH!
-THIS IS A SHOCK!
-DEFINITELY.
WHY'D YOU -- NO, DON'T, DUCK!
YOU MUSTN'T LOOK RIGHT THERE!
SEE?
-THANKS FOR YOUR BUSINESS!
-FAKIR.
-HE SMILED!
THAT TOTALLY RUINS
HIS BAD-BOY APPEAL.
-WE NEED HIM TO BECOME
A FULL-FLEDGED DELINQUENT!
-WHY IS SHE DEFANGING
THE BITINGLY SARCASTIC,
FANTASTIC FAKIR?!
-HUH?
-AN OLDER WOMAN LOVER, HUH?
-WE CAN'T SAY THAT
FOR CERTAIN YET!
-THAT'S RIGHT, DUCK!
YOU SHOULD HARBOR
UNREASONABLE HOPE!
-FIND THE TRUTH!
-STEP OUT BRAVELY!
-AAH!
[ WHIMPERS ]
-MY.
-HUH?
HEY.
-OH, HEY, FAKIR.
UM...
-ARE YOU A FRIEND OF FAKIR'S?
-CALLING HER JUST A FRIEND?
THAT'S SOME CONFIDENCE
SHE'S GOT THERE!
-OH, IT'S LIKE I CAN SEE
DUCK'S CRYING FACE BEFORE ME!
I CAN'T SIT ANY LONGER.
-WE WERE ALL JUST ON OUR WAY
TO THE ICE CREAM SHOP, RIGHT?
HUH?
UM, THEY WERE JUST HERE.
-YOU'RE AN INTERESTING PERSON.
MY NAME'S RAETSEL.
WHAT'S YOURS?
-UM, MINE'S DUCK.
-WELL, MISS DUCK,
FAKIR AND I ARE HEADING OVER
TO HIS HOUSE RIGHT NOW.
WOULD YOU LIKE TO COME ALONG?
-WHAT?
-RAETSEL.
-WHY NOT? RIGHT?
-UH...
-MM.
-I'M IMPRESSED
YOU FOUND WHERE I WAS.
-[ LAUGHS ]
YOU CAN'T HIDE ANYTHING FROM ME,
FAKIR.
-WELL, THERE'S STILL --
-FAKIR, WELCOME HOME.
HMM?
-IT'S BEEN A LONG TIME.
-RAETSEL!
-MAY I COME IN?
-OF COURSE.
[ TAPPING ]
-WHO DO YOU GO OUT WITH, ZURA?
IT'S A NEW LOVEY-DOVEY, ZURA!
-KARON, IS THIS YOUR...
-LAST I SAW YOU, MYTHO AND I
JUST ENTERED THE ACADEMY.
-THAT'S RIGHT.
I MUST ADMIT,
I WAS REALLY LONELY THEN.
HERE YOU GO.
-OH, THANKS.
-[ CHUCKLES ] IT'S ALL RIGHT.
I'M SOMETHING OF AN OLDER SISTER
TO FAKIR.
-REALLY?
I MEAN, NO,
I WASN'T REALLY SAYING --
-SHE'S BEEN LIKE A MOTHER,
EVER SINCE MY PARENTS DIED
AND I WAS TAKEN IN BY KARON.
-SISTER'S NOT LOVEY-DOVEY, ZURA?
-HUH?
-THEN IS RAETSEL
LOVEY-DOVEY WITH KA--
-[ CHUCKLES ] NOW, NOW, UZURUA.
-HOW FLATTERING.
WE LOOK THAT WAY?
THAT CERTAINLY WOULD BE NICE.
-YOU SHOULDN'T TEASE ADULTS
LIKE THAT, YOU KNOW.
-YOU ALWAYS TREAT ME AS A CHILD.
YOU KNOW, I'M AT AN AGE
WHERE MARRYING SOMEONE
WOULDN'T BE ODD.
-[ LAUGHS ]
WELL, AT MY AGE, ALL YOU
YOUNGSTERS LOOK THE SAME.
I STILL SEE YOU AS FAKIR
AND MYTHO'S PLAYMATE.
-THAT'S RIGHT. WHERE'S MYTHO?
-OH, YEAH. HE'S AT SCHOOL NOW.
HIS DANCING CONSUMES HIM.
-WEREN'T YOU ALWAYS WITH HIM,
SAYING,
"I'LL PROTECT YOU MYTHO"?
-AND I WILL.
YOU'RE STAYING HERE, RIGHT?
-ACTUALLY, I PLAN TO STAY
AT THE WATER MILL.
-I'LL WALK YOU THERE, THEN.
-THANK YOU, BUT...
I THINK I WANT TO TAKE
A LITTLE WALK WITH MISS DUCK.
-HUH?
-[ LAUGHS ]
I'M A TINY BIT JEALOUS.
FAKIR WITH A GIRL
AS CUTE AS YOU.
-OH, NO. I'M NOT CUTE AT ALL.
THE TRUTH IS,
I'M ALWAYS FIGHTING WITH FAKIR.
ACTUALLY, SOMETIMES I JUST CAN'T
STAND HIM, AND, YOU KNOW --
-[ CHUCKLES ]
I WONDER IF IT'S THANKS TO YOU
THAT FAKIR CHANGED SO MUCH.
-HUH?
-SAY, IS FAKIR
STILL WRITING STORIES?
-WRITING STORIES?
-THE STORIES THAT BOY
USED TO WRITE NOW AND AGAIN.
SOMETIMES THEY CAME TRUE.
-WHAT?
THE STORIES HE WROTE
ACTUALLY CAME TRUE?
-HE LOVED TO WRITE STORIES
FROM THE TIME HE WAS VERY SMALL.
THEY WERE
JUST SILLY LITTLE STORIES.
BUT SOMETIMES
PART OF THEM WOULD COME TRUE.
HOWEVER,
AFTER HE CAME TO KARON'S HOUSE,
HE JUST STOPPED WRITING
ALTOGETHER.
-MISS RAETSEL?
-I'VE SAID A LITTLE TOO MUCH.
I WONDER IF FAKIR WILL SCOLD ME.
[ CHUCKLES ]
-TO THINK FAKIR WROTE STORIES
AND THEY CAME TRUE!
IF HE CAN DO THAT...
MAYBE...
-MISS DUCK?
-OH, SORRY!
I JUST REMEMBERED SOMETHING!
UM, IT WAS FUN TALKING TO YOU!
-FAKIR HAS CHANGED.
NO.
THE ONE
WHO'S CHANGED THE MOST...IS ME.
-PROTECT, HUH?
HOW DO I PROTECT HIM?
WHO DO I FIGHT?
-YOU HAVE TO HELP ME, FAKIR.
MY HEART -- IT FEELS SO...
-THE STORY
NO LONGER HAS NEED OF YOU.
-THE FIGHT HAS BEGUN.
THE STORY IS MOVING.
WHETHER I'M HERE OR NOT.
BUT ALL I HAVE IS A SWORD.
[ CLANGING ]
-I'LL PROTECT MYTHO
WITH THIS SWORD.
-[ GASPS ] THERE YOU ARE!
[ BREATHING HEAVILY ]
HEY, FAKIR!
GUESS WHAT RAETSEL TOLD ME!
SHE SAID STORIES YOU WRITE
HAVE THE POWER TO COME TRUE!
-SHE WHAT?
-IF YOU REALLY HAVE THAT POWER
AND YOU WRITE A STORY WHERE
MYTHO GETS SAVED IN THE END --
FAKIR?
-WHAT ARE YOU SAYING?
-HUH?
I SAID I HEARD
SOME OF THE STORIES
YOU WROTE WHEN YOU WERE LITTLE
CAME TRUE.
SO --
-BE QUIET.
-HUH? BUT MYTHO COULD --
-SHUT UP!
-WHAT DO YOU MEAN?
WHY ARE YOU TALKING TO ME
THAT WAY?
HEY!
IF I REALLY COULD HELP MYTHO
BY MYSELF, FAKIR,
I WOULDN'T BE ASKING YOU.
BUT RIGHT NOW
I CAN'T DO ANYTHING.
-I SAID BE QUIET!
I'LL PROTECT MYTHO AS A KNIGHT.
END OF STORY.
I WON'T TAKE ORDERS FROM YOU!
-BUT --
FAKIR, WAIT! HEY! LISTEN TO ME!
FAKIR! COME ON, FAKIR!
IF YOU COULD HELP MYTHO,
THEN WHY WON'T YOU?
-[ PANTING ]
-WHAT'S WITH YOU TWO?
-[ LAUGHS ]
WE WERE WAITING SO WE'D BE READY
WHEN YOU CAME HOME CRYING.
-SO, WHAT HAPPENED
WITH THE WONDERFUL FAKIR?
-I DON'T CARE
WHAT HAPPENED TO HIM.
-GOOD, GOOD.
GET MAD AND CRY
AS MUCH AS YOU WANT.
-AND I THOUGHT WE'D BE ABLE
TO HELP MYTHO SOON.
WHY?
-BUT I DON'T UNDERSTAND.
-HE'S KIND OF SCARY.
-LATELY IT'S LIKE
HE'S A TOTALLY DIFFERENT PERSON.
-I'M GETTING SHIVERS
DOWN MY SPINE!
[ DRAMATIC MUSIC PLAYING ]
[ MUSIC STOPS,
ALL SCREAM ]
-RAETSEL.
-MYTHO, I'M JEALOUS OF YOU.
-OF ME?
-IF I COULD LIVE UNCHANGING
LIKE YOU --
-THAT'S NOT HOW IT IS.
SEE, I'M DIFFERENT
THAN I WAS BEFORE.
I'VE GOTTEN MY HEART BACK,
AND THAT MEANS...
NOW I CAN EVEN
ACCEPT YOUR LOVE FOR ME.
-[ CHUCKLES ]
NOW THAT'S SOME HAPPY NEWS.
MAYBE I'LL CALL OFF
THE WEDDING, THEN.
-WEDDING?!
AAH! THAT'S MR. MYTHO,
WHICH MEANS THE GIRL
IS MISS RUE!
THE TWO OF THEM
ARE GETTING MARRIED?
IS THAT RIGHT? GETTING MARRIED?
STUDENTS OF MINE
GETTING MARRIED BEFORE MY EYES?
THERE IS NO HAPPIER, MORE JOYFUL
THING FOR A TEACHER THAN THIS!
-CONGRATULATIONS.
-OH, THANK YOU.
-YOU DON'T LOOK VERY HAPPY.
COULD IT BE YOU'RE WAVERING?
-OF COURSE NOT.
I WAS ONLY JOKING BEFORE.
HANS LOVES ME DEEPLY
FROM THE BOTTOM OF HIS HEART.
WITH HIM, I'M SURE I CAN HAVE
A HAPPY LIFE.
[ GASPS ]
-COME, NOW.
YOU CAN'T LIE
TO YOUR OWN FEELINGS, RAETSEL.
YOU'VE GOT A PURE AND BEAUTIFUL
HEART, HAVEN'T YOU?
-I'M GOING NOW, MYTHO.
-I WILL HAVE YOU LOVE ME
AND ME ALONE!
SACRIFICE YOUR LIFE AND LOVE ME!
-IF I DO WHAT FATHER SAYS,
SOME DAY
HE'LL BE MY PRINCE ALONE.
RIGHT, FATHER?
-THE FIGHT
BETWEEN THE PRINCE AND THE RAVEN
IS BEING FOUGHT WITH FIERCER
AND FIERCER DESPERATION
IN A PLACE
WHERE NO ONE CAN SEE IT.
[ LAUGHS EVILLY ]
-SHE'S TOTALLY TOYING WITH HIM!
-THAT'S RIGHT.
A FAKIR PLAYED THOROUGHLY
BY AN ADULT WOMAN
AND THEN JUST TOSSED AWAY
LIKE YESTERDAY'S NEWSPAPER.
HOW WONDERFUL!
-FAKIR SAID
HE WOULD PROTECT MYTHO, SO WHY?
-I'LL PROTECT MYTHO AS A KNIGHT,
END OF STORY.
I WON'T TAKE ORDERS FROM YOU!
-AND IT WAS STARTING
TO LOOK LIKE
WE'D BE ABLE
TO WORK TOGETHER, TOO.
I DON'T LIKE THIS.
NO WAY
I'LL LET IT STAY LIKE THIS!
-HEY, WAIT!
-WHERE ARE YOU GOING, DUCK?!
-TIME FOR THE SECOND ROUND, HUH?
THAT DUCK REALLY DOES
LOVE BATTLES, DOESN'T SHE?!
-I SEE. SO, FAKIR SAID THAT.
-I WANT TO HELP SOMEONE.
AND HE'S SOMEONE IMPORTANT
TO FAKIR, TOO,
SO I THOUGHT
IF FAKIR WROTE A STORY,
MAYBE WE COULD HELP THIS PERSON,
BUT IT LOOKS LIKE --
-I'M SORRY.
THIS IS BECAUSE I'VE SAID
SOMETHING I SHOULDN'T HAVE.
-HUH?
-MISS DUCK, PLEASE.
WILL YOU PRETEND
THAT YOU NEVER HEARD
WHAT I TOLD YOU BEFORE?
-BUT SAVING THIS GUY
WILL MAKE FAKIR HAPPY, TOO!
-IN EXCHANGE, FAKIR WILL END UP
HURT AS WELL, THOUGH.
-WHAT?
-A LONG TIME AGO,
A LOT OF CROWS ONCE SHOWED UP
IN GOLD CROWN TOWN.
-CROWS?
-THE CROWS ATTACKED THE
TOWNSPEOPLE INDISCRIMINATELY.
FAKIR WAS A CHILD,
BUT HE MUST HAVE WANTED TO DO
SOMETHING TO HELP.
HE WROTE A STORY WHERE HE BECAME
A HERO AND DEFEATED THE CROWS.
AND THEN,
JUST LIKE FAKIR HAD WRITTEN,
THE CROWS CAME AND ATTACKED HIM.
BUT THE ENDING WAS DIFFERENT
THAN HIS STORY.
AFTERWARDS, HE GOT
SO HE NEVER TALKED ABOUT IT,
AS IF HE SEALED
THOSE MEMORIES AWAY.
HE STOPPED WRITING STORIES, TOO.
-I NEVER KNEW
FAKIR HAD SOMETHING LIKE THAT
HAPPEN TO HIM.
-IT MUST STILL CUT HIM DEEPLY,
AND YET I -- MISS DUCK, PLEASE.
GIVE FAKIR SOME SPACE.
WHAT IN THE WORLD AM I DOING?
[ DOOR OPENS ]
[ GASPS ]
-I CAME TO GET YOU, RAETSEL.
MY BEAUTIFUL BRIDE.
[ DRUM BANGING ]
-LOVEY-DOVEY!
LOVEY-DOVEY!
LOVE -- HUH?
DUCK, WHAT'S WRONG, ZURA?
-I'M THE WORST.
WHAT SHOULD I SAY TO FAKIR?
-YOU WANT TO SAY SOMETHING
TO FAKIR, ZURA?
WOW! LOTS OF CROWS, ZURA!
-THE WATER MILL!
COULD MYTHO
BE TRYING TO GET RAETSEL?
-RAETSEL, I'LL GIVE YOU A LOVE
WITH NO WAVERING.
YOU'LL LOVE ONLY ME, WON'T YOU?
-YES. MYTHO.
-[ CHUCKLES ] MY RAETSEL.
COME HERE AND GIVE
YOUR BEAUTIFUL HEART TO ME!
-I AM MYTHO'S BRIDE.
-WAIT.
-WHO ARE YOU?
-I AM KNOWN AS PRINCESS TUTU.
PLEASE COME AND DANCE WITH ME.
WON'T YOU, MISS RAETSEL?
-PRINCESS TUTU?
-IF YOU REALLY HAVE THAT POWER
AND YOU WRITE A STORY WHERE
MYTHO GETS SAVED IN THE END --
-WHAT IS THIS AWFUL FEELING?
THE POWER
TO MAKE STORIES COME TRUE?
A POWER LIKE THAT IN ME?
-LOVEY-DOVEY! LOVEY-DOVEY!
LOVEY-DOVEY!
-THAT'S RIDICULOUS.
-LOVEY-DOVEY! FAKIR!
-HUH?
-IS IT MYTHO THAT MISS RAETSEL
IS LOVEY-DOVEY WITH, ZURA?
-[ GASPS ]
-THAT'S A LOVELY WEDDING DRESS.
YOU HAVE SOMEONE
YOU'RE ENGAGED TO, RIGHT?
THEN WHY ARE YOU --
-KARON KNOWS HOW I FEEL,
BUT WHEN I SAW HIM,
HE SAID NOTHING.
HE DID NOTHING.
-OH.
-HANS, HOWEVER, HE ASSURES ME
OF HIS LOVE FOR ME.
HE LOOKS ONLY AT ME
AND HOLDS ME CLOSE,
AND I LOVE HIM DEARLY, AS WELL.
YET NO MATTER WHAT I DO,
I SEE KARON'S FACE IN MY MIND.
-YOU'RE SUFFERING BECAUSE YOU'RE
WAVERING BETWEEN TWO LOVES.
LOVE ONLY ME
AND YOUR WAVERING WILL VANISH.
-YOU MUSTN'T GO THERE.
DOES WAVERING SCARE YOU?
IT'S SOMETHING YOU FEEL
BECAUSE YOU TRULY LOVE PEOPLE.
-WHAT SCARES ME
IS THAT I MAY STILL LOVE KARON.
WHEN THAT THOUGHT
CROSSES MY MIND,
BEING WITH HIM IS --
IT'S PAINFUL.
-KARON?
-I DON'T WANT TO WAVER!
-RAETSEL.
-THAT'S RIGHT.
IF YOU LOVE ONLY ME.
-IF I BUT LOVE ONLY MYTHO.
-NO! YOU'RE MAKING
A GRAVE MISTAKE, MISS RAETSEL!
-JUST FORGET EVERYTHING ELSE
AND LOVE ONLY ME!
-BOTH OF THESE THINGS REFLECT
YOUR TRUE HEART, MISS RAETSEL,
BUT IS WHAT YOU ARE GRASPING AT
RIGHT NOW YOUR TRUE FEELINGS?
-TRUE AND FALSE
HAVE NOTHING TO DO WITH IT.
PEOPLE JUST LOVE OTHERS
BECAUSE THEY WANT TO BE LOVED.
SHE WAVERS BECAUSE SHE WONDERS
WHICH ONE WILL LOVE HER MORE!
-THAT PAIN IS HOW
YOU TRULY FEEL, SO WAKE UP!
YOU WANT TO BE HAPPY
WITH THE ONE YOU LOVE MOST,
DON'T YOU?
-I KEPT ON WEIGHING THEIR LOVES
AGAINST EACH OTHER
FOR THE SAKE
OF MY OWN HAPPINESS.
TO ESCAPE THE ACHING PAIN
OF MY WAVERING,
I SET OUT TO GET FAKIR
TO WRITE A STORY ABOUT ME.
EVEN THOUGH
I KNEW IT WOULD HURT HIM.
I'M A HORRIBLE WOMAN.
-TO WANT TO BE LOVED
BY THOSE WE LOVE
IS NOT AN EVIL FEELING.
I'M SURE IT HURTS
TO WAVER BETWEEN TWO LOVES,
BUT SIMPLY RUNNING AWAY WON'T
HELP YOU TO ESCAPE THAT PAIN.
-NO, YOU --
YOU SHOULD BE LOVING ONLY ME!
RAETSEL!
-MYTHO, I WILL NOT ALLOW YOU
TO HARM RAETSEL.
-[ CHUCKLES ]
HOW INTERESTING.
[ WHOOSHING ]
[ CHUCKLES ]
-STOP!
THE TWO OF YOU FIGHTING,
IT'S NOT GOING TO --
[ GASPS ]
-MYTHO, DO YOU FEEL NOTHING?
YOU WOULD EVEN USE RAETSEL?
-[ LAUGHS ]
I WAS MERELY TRYING TO SAVE HER!
-FAKIR!
[ BOTH GRUNT ]
-TRYING TO SAVE HER?
DON'T SUGARCOAT THINGS.
-WHAT? LIKE YOU'VE DONE
WITH YOUR SERVICE?
KNIGHTS WHO CAN'T EVEN DIE
SHOULDN'T POINT FINGERS.
PATHETIC.
HOW LONG WILL YOU GO ON
SHAMING YOURSELF?
WIELDING THAT PLAY SWORD
OF YOURS.
-MYTHO, STOP IT!
[ BOTH GRUNT ]
YOU KNOW YOU CAN'T
LAY A FINGER ON ME, FAKIR.
-THIS SWORD ISN'T
FOR SLAYING YOU WITH, MYTHO.
NOW, WAKE UP!
REMEMBER YOUR TRUE SELF, MYTHO!
-[ GASPS ]
-MYTHO!
-STOP IT.
SHUT UP.
SHUT UP!
AAH!
-FAKIR!
-HUH?
-STOP IT. DON'T HURT FAKIR.
YOU HEAR ME, RAVEN? STOP THIS.
-MYTHO?
-RUN.
DON'T -- DON'T COME NEAR ME.
[ GROANS ]
-MYTHO.
-RAETSEL. RAETSEL.
-FAKIR, I -- I'M SORRY.
PLEASE FORGIVE ME.
I WAS THINKING ONLY OF MYSELF.
ALL I WANTED
WAS TO ESCAPE MY PAIN.
AND I DID SOMETHING TO HURT YOU.
I'M SORRY.
-IT'S ALL RIGHT.
I'VE ALREADY FORGIVEN YOU,
RAETSEL.
-EVEN THOUGH MISS RAETSEL
WAS SUFFERING SO MUCH,
SHE TOLD ME -- SHE TOLD ME
THAT I OUGHT TO GIVE YOU
SOME SPACE,
AND THAT'S THE TRUTH.
IT WASN'T IN MISS RAETSEL'S
HEART TO HURT YOU, FAKIR.
FAKIR?
-PLEASE TAKE CARE OF RAETSEL.
-FAKIR.
IT WASN'T IN MISS RAETSEL'S
HEART TO HURT YOU.
-DON'T HURT FAKIR.
YOU HEAR ME, RAVEN?
STOP THIS!
-IF I REALLY COULD HELP MYTHO
BY MYSELF, FAKIR,
I WOULDN'T BE ASKING YOU.
BUT RIGHT NOW
I CAN'T DO ANYTHING.
-WHAT CAN I DO?
THAT'S RIGHT.
I CAN WRITE A LETTER
TO THE PRESIDENT.
-FAKIR? BUT, WAIT, YOU'RE --
-RAETSEL.
-RAETSEL!
-OH, GOOD MORNING.
WHAT'S THAT IN YOUR HAND?
DID YOU WRITE A STORY FOR ME?
KARON, I WANTED TO TELL YOU.
HANS AND I
ARE GOING TO GET MARRIED.
-HUH?
-SO I SEE. CONGRATULATIONS.
-RAETSEL.
-YOU SEE, I REALIZED
WHAT I WANTED
WAS TO SAY A PROPER GOODBYE
TO KARON.
BUT I'LL TAKE THIS.
THANKS SO MUCH.
-YOUR STORY
DIDN'T COME TRUE, HUH?
-NO, IT DIDN'T.
-HMM.
-I THINK I WILL TRY WRITING ONE.
-WHAT?
-YOU KNOW, A STORY ABOUT MYTHO.
-THAT'S DANGEROUS.
THAT POWER IS TRULY DANGEROUS,
YOU KNOW?
CAN SOMEONE LIKE YOU,
WHO COULDN'T ATTAIN
MERE KNIGHTHOOD,
REALLY MASTER
SUCH A POTENT CRAFT?
[ LAUGHS EVILLY ]
[ SOFT MUSIC PLAYS ]
-[ SINGING IN JAPANESE ]
[ SINGING IN JAPANESE
CONTINUES ]
-THEY TOOK OUT THE ENDINGS
TO STOP THEM FROM BECOMING REAL?
-HE'S AWAKENED.
THIS IS DANGEROUS!
-IT SEEMS HE'S GAINED
THE KNOWLEDGE, BUT THAT'S ALL.
-A DIRECT DESCENDENT
OF DROSSELMEYER'S,
AND THIS IS YOUR LEVEL?
-THAT HURTS!
-YOU HESITATED TO TAKE MY HAND.
-MYTHO WAS ALWAYS KIND TO RUE,
BUT...
-TO THOSE WHO ACCEPT EVERYTHING,
HAPPINESS.
TO THOSE WHO RESIST EVERYTHING,
GLORY.
-FAKIR, PLEASE.
YOU MUST WAKE UP!
-ALL YOU CHILDREN
WHO LOVE STORIES,
COME GATHER 'ROUND.
[ LAUGHS EVILLY ]