-ONCE UPON A TIME,
THERE WAS A MAIDEN.
THE MAIDEN
WORE TATTERED CLOTHES
AND WAS CALLED CINDERELLA.
BUT WITH THE HELP
OF SOME MAGIC,
SHE BECAME A BEAUTIFUL PRINCESS
AND GOT TO DANCE
WITH THE PRINCE.
THEN AT THE STROKE OF MIDNIGHT,
THE MAIDEN RAN AWAY,
LEAVING A GLASS SLIPPER,
AND SHE RETURNED TO BEING
CINDERELLA ONCE AGAIN.
THE PRINCE WENT TO GREAT
LENGTHS TO FIND THIS MAIDEN,
WHICH HE DID,
AND TOOK HER AS HIS WIFE.
YET A THORNY QUESTION ARISES.
DID THE PRINCE REALLY FALL
IN LOVE WITH THE MAIDEN?
[ RITSUKO OKAZAKI'S
"MORNING GRACE" PLAYING ]
-♪ YONDE IRU KOE ♪
♪ SAA ME O SAMASHITE ♪
♪ NAKIGAO NUGUTTE ♪
♪ MABUSHII HIKARI ♪
♪ KIGI NO TSUYU ♪
♪ UMARERU ♪
♪ DARE MO SHIRANAI ♪
♪ HIMITSU NO MIZUBE DE ♪
♪ ODORE INOCHI NO PA DO DU ♪
♪ KYOU MO YUME MITERU ♪
♪ SORE WA YASASHIKU ♪
♪ HAGESHII NAGARE NE ♪
♪ DOKO MADE TSUZUKU RABIRINSU ♪
♪ WATASHI WA YUKOU ♪
♪ NIGIRISHIMERU YUME ♪
[ TCHAIKOVSKY'S
"WALTZ OF THE FLOWERS" PLAYING ]
- THAT'S RIGHT. I AM A CROW.
AND I ALONE AM
THE TRUE PRIMA DONNA,
PRINCESS KRAEHE.
I TAKE WHAT I DESIRE BY FORCE
IF NEED BE.
-PRINCESS TUTU,
WILL YOU NOT CEASE THIS
RESTORING OF HIS HEART, THEN?
-NO, BECAUSE THAT IS
THE PRINCE'S WISH.
[ GLASS CRUNCHES ]
-DO YOU INTEND TO SHATTER
HIS HEART AGAIN?
-IF I DO...
-I WON'T ALLOW YOU TO.
-YOU'LL KILL ME THEN?
-WHAT?
-COULD YOU KILL?
-THAT'S...NOT --
-[ BOTH GRUNT ]
-[ GASPS ]
-STOP!
-AND WHEN THE RAVEN
STANDS BEFORE YOU, STRIKE!
YOU CAN'T GUARD MYTHO
WITH JUST HEART SHARDS.
-BUT KRAEHE --
SHE WAS SUFFERING.
-THEN THAT WAS YOUR CHANCE.
I WOULD HAVE FINISHED HER,
AND IF IT CAME DOWN TO IT,
I COULD EVEN KILL YOU, TOO.
-TUTU, RUN.
-[ GASPS ]
[ CRYING ]
[ RAPID FOOTSTEPS DEPART ]
-WHY MUST YOU HINDER ME
FROM REGAINING MY HEART, FAKIR?
-HINDER?
-MY HEART.
I WANT TO GET MY HEART BACK,
NO MATTER WHAT FATE
MIGHT THEN AWAIT ME.
I JUST... [ GASPS ] FAKIR.
YOU'RE TREMBLING.
WHY?
[ DOOR OPENS ]
[ TINKLES ]
-IS THAT...
-WHY? WHEN IN THE WORLD DID
I GO BACK TO BEING A DUCK?
I KNOW!
[ GRUNTS ]
[ GASPS ] WHY? WHY DON'T I TURN
BACK INTO A GIRL?!
[ BLADE ZINGS ]
-THE PENDANT!
-THIS IS GOOD, LITTLE DUCK.
AFTER ALL, THERE'S NOTHING
MORE BORING
THAN A PERFECT HEROINE.
WHEN THE SPELL'S BROKEN,
DUCK IS JUST A DUCK.
NOW SHOW US WHAT THE DUCK
WILL DO,
WHAT ONLY A DUCK IS CAPABLE OF.
[ LAUGHS EVILLY ]
- OH! WHAT DO I DO?
WITHOUT THE PENDANT,
I CAN'T BECOME A GIRL
OR PRINCESS TUTU.
WHERE COULD IT HAVE GONE?!
MY PENDANT!
-[ Thinking ] YOU JUST TRY
AND COME FOR IT, PRINCESS TUTU.
-FAKIR, YOU'RE TREMBLING.
[ GASPS ]
[ LANTERN RATTLES ]
-ABSURD.
[ BIRDS CHIRPING ]
[ WATER STREAMING ]
-[ Thinking ] WHERE ARE YOU,
PRINCESS TUTU?
-[ SNORING ]
- HEY.
[ FOOTSTEPS APPROACH ]
-[ CONTINUES SNORING ]
-HEY!
-HUH? WHAT? [ SCREECHING ]
[ Thinking ] OH, NO!
I MUST HAVE FALLEN ASLEEP!
-YOU'RE THAT DUCK
FROM THE OTHER DAY.
-OH! THE PENDANT!
[ GASPS AND MOANS ]
-WHAT IS IT?
HAVE YOU TAKEN A LIKING TO THIS?
-QUACK! HUH?
QUACK! QUACK!
-I DO ENVY YOUR INNOCENCE.
-[ GASPS ]
[ WHIMPERS ] QUACK.
HUH? QUACK!
[ TCHAIKOVSKY'S "DANCE OF
THE SUGAR PLUM FAIRY" PLAYING ]
♪
QUACK!
[ Thinking ] HE'S WEARING IT!
[ GROANS ]
-[ Thinking ]
PERHAPS PRINCESS TUTU'S
AMONG THESE GIRLS.
-[ SNIFFS ]
MR. CAT, DO YOU SMELL THAT?
I SMELL A TASTY DUCK!
-HUSH, MISS CROCODELIA.
-[ Thinking ]
I'M THINKING TOO HARD.
MYTHO'S SO HANDSOME.
HE WAS ALWAYS HANDSOME,
BUT NOW HE'S EVEN MORE.
IS IT 'CAUSE HE'S GOT
SOME OF HIS FEELINGS BACK?
-HE'S SO HANDSOME, ISN'T HE?
-DUCK WILL BE SAD
SHE MISSED IT!
-SHE MUST BE HURTING PRETTY BAD
FROM THE REJECTION, HUH?
-I'D LOVE IT IF SHE IS.
-I HOPE SHE'S COMING BACK
TO CLASS SOON.
-RIGHT, RIGHT,
BEFORE SHE FULLY RECOVERS.
-WELL, YOU KNOW,
SHE DOES RECOVER QUICKLY.
-NO!
-MISS PIKE, MISS LILIE,
IF YOU CONTINUE TO CHITCHAT
DURING CLASS,
I WILL HAVE THE BOTH OF YOU
MARRY ME TOGETHER!
-[ BOTH GASP ]
-WELL, WHILE WE'RE AT IT,
WHY NOT INCLUDE MISS DUCK,
WHO IS ABSENT TODAY,
SO ALL THREE OF YOU CAN GET
MARRIED TOGETHER?! [ HISSES ]
-[ GASPING ]
-[ SLURPING AND GROWLING ]
-YOU DANCED SPLENDIDLY,
MR. MYTHO.
YOU'RE BEGINNING TO CONVEY MORE
EMOTION OVER STRAIGHT TECHNIQUE.
-YES, SIR.
-SO, YOU'RE IN LOVE?
-AM I?
-I CAN TELL, YOU SEE.
-IN LOVE?
-VERY WELL.
I WILL HOLD A SPECIAL CLASS
ON BEING IN LOVE AFTER SCHOOL
FOR YOU.
-[ Thinking ] MYTHO'S IN...
-YES, SIR.
-BEING IN LOVE
IS A WONDERFUL THING,
BUT THERE ARE SOME THINGS
YOU MUST BE CAREFUL ABOUT.
IN PARTICULAR, DURING PUBERTY,
SELF-CONTROL IS IMPORTANT.
[ BIRDS CHIRPING ]
-[ GRUNTS ]
QUACK!
[ Thinking ]
THE PENDANT, THE PENDANT!
[ SHOWER RUNNING ]
-[ Thinking ] IT'S NOT HERE!
DON'T TELL ME HE TOOK IT
IN THERE WITH HIM! OH!
[ SHOWER TURNS OFF ]
-QUACK!
HERE HE COMES!
WHAT DO I DO?! WHAT DO I DO?!
QUACK!
[ GRUNTS ]
[ GASPS ]
[ Thinking ] HUH?
SO HE DID HAVE IT!
IS HE INJURED?
NO, IT'S A BIRTHMARK.
-[ GRUNTS ]
-[ SIGHS DEEPLY ]
-[ Thinking ] THE PENDANT --
IF I COULD JUST REACH IT!
[ GRUNTS ] OH!
-MYTHO, YOU REALLY
DON'T KNOW ANYTHING
ABOUT REGAINING YOUR HEART
AND WHAT THAT ENTAILS.
-[ Thinking ] WHAT?
[ WINGS FLAPPING ]
-[ GASPS ]
HUH?
-HUH?
-THAT DAMNED KRAEHE.
IS THIS TO SAY SHE DOESN'T
SEE ME AS A THREAT?!
-[ Thinking ]
MYTHO AND KRAHE'S WEDDING,
WITH FAKIR FOR A WITNESS. OH.
[ WINGS FLAPPING ]
[ BELL TOLLING ]
-TONIGHT AT MIDNIGHT...
AT THE CHURCH.
[ CAWING ]
[ GRUNTS ]
[ CROWS CAWING IN DISTANCE ]
-WHAT'S FAKIR...
THE SMITH?
QUACK!
[ CLATTERS ]
[ DOOR OPENS ]
-KARON.
-FAKIR.
-WHERE IS THE SWORD?
-YOU HAVEN'T BEEN HOME IN AGES,
YET NO GREETINGS FOR ME?
THERE ARE PLENTY OF SWORDS
IN THE SHOP.
-NO, THAT SWORD.
THE LOHENGRIN SWORD.
-[ GASPS ]
-I HAVE NEED OF IT.
I HAVE TO PROTECT MYTHO
FROM THE CROWS NOW.
-I CAN'T GIVE IT TO YOU.
-WHAT?
-YOU KNOW THAT SWORD IS MEANT
FOR THE KNIGHT.
-YOU PROMISED THAT YOU WOULD
LET ME HAVE IT.
-THAT WAS WHEN YOU WERE A CHILD.
-MYTHO HAS BEEN REGAINING
HIS HEART.
-[ GASPS ]
-AND PRINCESS TUTU
HAS ALREADY APPEARED.
THE CROWS ARE RETURNING AS WELL.
THE LEGEND YOU TOLD ME ABOUT
AS A CHILD
IS SWIFTLY BECOMING REALITY.
IF SO, THIS MEANS
THAT I AM THE KNIGHT
FROM THE STORY REBORN.
-[ Thinking ]
FAKIR IS THE KNIGHT REBORN?
[ "MARCH" FROM TCHAIKOVSKY'S
"THE NUTCRACKER" PLAYING ]
-IF I'M THE KNIGHT,
IT SHOULD BE FINE IF I USE
THE LOHENGRIN SWORD.
-FAKIR, WHY CAN'T YOU
JUST LEAVE MYTHO BE?
-LEAVE HIM BE?
-HE WOULD BE MUCH BETTER OFF
FORGETTING THIS ACCURSED TALE.
-IT'S TOO LATE TO BE
SAYING THINGS LIKE THAT.
-[ WHIMPERS ]
-[ SIGHS ]
IT WAS ON THE SAME DAY
THAT YOU TOOK ME IN
AFTER MY PARENTS DIED
WHEN YOU TOLD ME, REMEMBER?
-THIS MARK OF YOURS IS THE SAME
AS IN THE LEGEND
THAT HAS BEEN PASSED DOWN
AMONG OUR PEOPLE.
I'M SURE YOU'LL GROW
TO BE STRONG.
IT'S A SIGN THAT
YOU'RE THE REINCARNATION
OF THE BRAVE KNIGHT
WHO GUARDED THE PRINCE.
-[ GIGGLES ]
-IN TIME, IT BECAME
A SOURCE OF PRIDE FOR ME.
IF IT WAS TO PROTECT THE PEOPLE,
THE PRINCE NEVER FEARED BEING
INJURED IN THE LINE OF DUTY.
WOW. THAT'S GREAT.
AND THEN MY DESTINY
WAS SUDDENLY SET IN MOTION.
HMM?
KARON, HIS HEART --
I DON'T THINK IT'S BEATING.
-HUH?
[ GASPS ]
-KARON?
-[ GRUNTS ]
-[ GASPS ]
-[ GRUNTS AND EXHALES ]
-[ BOTH GASP ]
-THE PRINCE WHO HAD
LOST HIS HEART.
-HUH?
-MYTHOS.
-"MYTHOS" MEANS A PERSON
OR CHARACTER FROM A LEGEND.
-DID YOU KNOW?
-NO.
-YOU DON'T KNOW ANYTHING,
DO YOU, PRINCE?
-SORRY.
-"PRINCE" IS A WEIRD NAME.
HOW ABOUT WE CALL YOU "MYTHO"?
NOW THAT WOULD BE A COOL NAME.
-OKAY.
-ALL RIGHT!
YOU'LL BE "MYTHO"
STARTING TODAY.
MYTHO HAD NO EMOTIONS,
BUT WHENEVER HE SAW
SOMETHING WEAK SUFFERING,
NO MATTER THE DANGER, HE WOULD
RUSH TO TRY AND PROTECT IT.
-[ CROWD GASPING ]
-UH, MYTHO, IT'S DANGEROUS!
MYTHO! [ GASPS ]
-[ CROWD MURMURING ]
[ CROWD SCREAMING ]
-[ GASPS ] MYTHO!
-FAKIR.
-STUPID.
YOU DON'T THINK, DO YOU?
YOU DO USELESS THINGS LIKE THAT.
-SORRY.
-FORGET HELPING OTHER PEOPLE.
-YES.
-YOU JUST LISTEN TO WHAT
I TELL YOU.
FROM NOW ON,
I'LL BE PROTECTING YOU.
I WILL PROTECT MYTHO.
THAT WAS THE PROMISE I MADE.
-[ Thinking ] PROTECT MYTHO?
BUT THEN WHY DID YOU TRY
TO SHATTER HIS HEART?
-THIS FOOL'S ERRAND
THAT YOU'RE ATTEMPTING NOW
IS NOT FOR MYTHO'S SAKE.
IT'S FOR YOUR OWN SAKE,
ISN'T IT, FAKIR?
-WHAT?
-THE TIME TO FIGHT
IS DRAWING CLOSER.
ARE YOU SURE
YOU'RE NOT AFRAID OF SHARING
IN THE SAME WRETCHED FATE
AS THE KNIGHT FROM THE STORY?
-[ GASPS ]
I'M NOT.
-YOU KEPT CALLING THE PRINCE
A GOOD-FOR-NOTHING
TO MAKE SURE HIS HEART
WOULDN'T BE RESTORED.
KNOWING HE LOVED TO DANCE,
YOU ENROLLED HIM AT THE ACADEMY
TO KEEP HIM BUSY.
YOU WERE TOO AFRAID TO FIGHT.
-NO!
-THERE'S NO WAY
THAT YOU'LL PROTECT MYTHO
THE WAY YOU ARE NOW!
-STOP IT!
-JUST GIVE IT UP!
-ENOUGH! ANY SWORD WILL DO.
-[ BLADE ZINGS ]
-[ GASPS AND GRUNTS ]
-[ CRIES ]
[ THUD ]
-[ WHIMPERS ]
-THIS ENDS NOW, GOT IT?
-YES. I MAY BE AFRAID
OF RISKING MY LIFE
JUST AS YOU'VE ACCUSED ME,
BUT I WANT TO PROTECT HIM.
THE PURE-HEARTED MYTHO
WHO'S ALWAYS RISKED HIMSELF.
-[ GASPS ]
THERE'S A SHARD AROUND HERE
SOMEWHERE.
-[ GASPS ]
-FAKIR!
[ RAPID FOOTSTEPS DEPART ]
[ DOOR OPENS AND CLOSES ]
[ SIGHS ]
-[ SOBBING ]
-[ Thinking ]
I DON'T KNOW ANYMORE
WHAT'S RIGHT, WHAT'S WRONG.
THE ONLY THING I CAN TELL
IS FAKIR ISN'T LYING.
I DIDN'T SEE IT,
BUT THIS WHOLE TIME,
FAKIR'S BEEN THE SAME AS ME.
NO, HE MIGHT CARE ABOUT MYTHO
EVEN MORE THAN I DO.
[ WATER RIPPLING ]
-OH, IT'S YOU.
SORRY YOU'VE CAUGHT ME
IN A BAD MOMENT.
-QUACK.
-YOU'RE CRYING.
WHAT, FOR MY SAKE?
-HUH?
OH.
-QUACK?
-TAKE IT.
YOU WANTED IT, DIDN'T YOU?
[ Thinking ] I WILL NOT
ACKNOWLEDGE YOU, PRINCESS TUTU.
[ BIRD TWEETING ]
-[ Thinking ] FAKIR.
OH, THAT'S RIGHT! THERE'S
A SHARD AT KARON'S HOUSE!
[ DOG BARKING IN DISTANCE ]
-WAS THIS REALLY
THE RIGHT THING TO DO?
-THERE'S NO WAY TO KNOW THAT.
NO MATTER WHAT YOU DO,
YOU'LL ONLY REGRET IT.
-YOU'RE RIGHT.
[ CLATTER ]
-[ Thinking ]
JUST AS I THOUGHT.
[ CLANKING ]
-COME. IF YOU DON'T HURRY,
THE WEDDING WILL START
WITHOUT YOU.
[ LAUGHING EVILLY ]
[ TINKLING ]
[ TINKLING CONTINUES ]
-MR. KARON.
-[ GASPS ]
PRINCESS TUTU?
COULD IT REALLY BE?
-PLEASE, COME DANCE WITH ME...
MR. KARON.
-SO THE TALE TRULY HAS SPRUNG
BACK TO LIFE HERE IN OUR DAY.
BUT I STILL DO NOT KNOW
WHAT IT IS I SHOULD DO.
WE'VE ALWAYS REGRETTED
TELLING FAKIR THE LEGEND.
I REGRET HAVING HURT FAKIR.
THE ONLY THINGS I CAN DO
FOR THAT CHILD
ARE THINGS THAT I REGRET.
-NO. YOU SHOULD BE ABLE
TO HAVE FAITH IN HIM.
-OH. HAVE FAITH IN HIM?
-YES. IF FAKIR JOURNEYS
DOWN THE PATH
OF HIS HEART'S CONVICTION,
I DO NOT BELIEVE HE'LL
REGRET IT, WHATEVER THE OUTCOME.
WHY NOT HAVE FAITH IN FAKIR?
HAVE FAITH IN...FAKIR.
-I AM THE FEELING OF REGRET.
[ TINKLES ]
-PRINCESS TUTU, THANK YOU.
MY DOUBTS HAVE CLEARED.
-[ Thinking ] A BOOK IS NOT
A THING TO BE FEARED.
TURN THIS PAGE
WITH YOUR OWN HAND.
[ PAGE FLIPS ]
-[ GASPS ] AAH!
[ CLANKING ]
-[ GASPS ] NO WAY.
NO WAY WILL I SUCCUMB
TO SUCH A MISERABLE FATE.
I'LL CHANGE IT.
[ WATER FALLING ]
-MY PRINCE.
-PRINCESS TUTU.
-I'VE BROUGHT YOU A SHARD
OF YOUR HEART.
-THANK YOU.
-ARE YOU GOING TO KRAEHE?
-YES, I FEEL I MUSTN'T RUN AWAY.
-[ CHUCKLES ]
THANK YOU, PRINCESS TUTU,
FOR GOING TO THE TROUBLE
OF RETURNING THE SHARDS
OF MY HUSBAND'S HEART.
BUT WHETHER YOU RETURN THEM
OR NOT MAKES NO DIFFERENCE NOW,
FOR THE PRINCE
WILL BECOME MINE TONIGHT.
I WILL HAVE YOU BEAR WITNESS
AS A NUPTIAL SACRIFICE.
[ DOOR CREAKS ]
-I'VE BEEN WAITING.
DO WHAT YOU MUST.
-[ GASPS ]
-LEAVE NO CAUSE FOR REGRET.
-KARON.
[ CLATTER ]
-[ GASPS ]
-GO, MY SON.
-UM...
-WHAT SAY YOU, PRINCESS TUTU?
AREN'T WE JUST PERFECT
FOR EACH OTHER?
[ WINGS FLAP ]
[ RAVENS CAWING ]
-[ GASPS ]
-[ GIGGLES ] I'VE PREPARED
A SPECIAL SEAT FOR YOU.
-TUTU. [ GASPS ]
-FIRST, WE'LL HAVE A DANCE.
I COULD DO AWAY WITH TUTU
THIS VERY SECOND,
BUT LET'S CELEBRATE.
[ PROKOFIEV'S "CINDERELLA,
OP. 87:19" PLAYING ]
-MYTHO.
-MY BEAUTIFUL PRINCE,
YOU ARE MINE.
-KRAEHE, WHO ARE YOU?
WHY MUST YOU DEMAND I BE YOURS?
-BECAUSE IT IS FATE.
-FATE? WHOSE FATE IS THAT?
-[ GIGGLES ] IT MATTERS NOT
WHOSE FATE IT IS.
FATE CANNOT BE CHANGED,
NOT BY ANYONE.
[ CRASH ]
-[ GASPS ]
[ HOOVES CLOPPING ]
-BACK, YOU FILTHY RAVEN!
-FAKIR.
[ HORSE WHINNIES ]
-SO, THE COWARD HAS ARRIVED.
-FAKIR!
[ BLADE ZINGS ]
-I WILL SUFFER YOU
TO BE NEAR MYTHO NO MORE!
[ RAVENS CAWING ]
-[ GRUNTS ]
-KRAEHE, STOP!
-WHAT'S WRONG?
WHY ARE YOU IN SUCH PAIN?
[ CAWING ]
-OH!
[ TINKLES ]
-[ Thinking ]
SHE HAS THE STONE BACK.
-WHAT IS IT?! HURRY AND BEGONE,
OR DO YOU HAVE A BURNING DESIRE
TO SETTLE THINGS NOW?!
-I DON'T HAVE ANY WISH
TO FIGHT YOU.
[ BELL TOLLING ]
-I HAVE TO HURRY,
OR FAKIR AND MYTHO
ARE GONNA CATCH UP TO ME!
-OHH! AAH! UHH!
[ THUD ]
-OH, IF I'M CAUGHT
WANDERING OUT THIS LATE,
THEY'LL BE SUSPI--
[ GATE CREAKS ]
-WHAT?! NO WAY!
[ SQUEAKING ]
-HEY, YOU.
-[ GASPS ]
-TEE-HEE.
-TEE-HEE NOTHING. WHAT ARE YOU
DOING OUT THIS LATE?
-WHAT AM I -- WHAT AM I DOING?
WELL, IF I'M OUT THIS LATE,
WHAT ELSE COULD I BE DOING
BUT THAT?
-THAT?
-YOU KNOW, THAT.
WELL, SEE YA.
-HEY, WHAT'S ON YOUR --
[ TINKLES ]
-WHAT? WAIT!
THAT PENDANT.
-GOOD NIGHT, FAKIR! WHOA! OH!
-PRINCESS TUTU?
-WHAT DO I DO?
COULD IT BE HE'S FOUND OUT?
-OH, DEAR. IT WOULD APPEAR
THAT YOUR IDENTITY
HAS BEEN FOUND.
WHAT WILL YOU DO, PRINCESS TUTU?
[ CHUCKLES EVILLY ]
[ RITSUKO OKAZAKI'S "ALTHOUGH
MY LOVE IS SMALL" PLAYING ]
-♪ YUME MIRU ♪
♪ YOU NI ♪
♪ KOI O SHITA NO ♪
♪ FUKURAMU ♪
♪ KOKORO GA FUKURAMU NO YO ♪
♪ IKITERUTTE SUTEKI
NA KOTO TO OMOTTA ♪
♪ ASU GA MACHI DOOSHII ♪
♪ MM ♪
♪ ANATA NO CHIKARA NI NARITAI
NO DONNA TOKI NI MO WATASHI ♪
♪ MATTE MATTE
KURENAI HASHITTE ♪
♪ HASHITTE IKU NO YO ♪
♪ KAZE MO AMAGUMO
MO OIKOSHITE ♪
♪ WATASHI DAKE
NO TSUBASA HABATAITE ♪
-I'M SURPRISED, TO BE HONEST.
OF ALL THE PEOPLE,
I NEVER EXPECTED IT WAS YOU.
-TELL ME, DUCK,
DO YOU KNOW ABOUT TUTU?
-THE ONE MYTHO WANTS TO SEE
ISN'T ME.
IT'S PRINCESS TUTU, BUT --
I WISH I COULD HAVE
STAYED RUE FOREVER,
FREE OF KRAEHE'S MEMORIES,
BUT NOW --
-THE NAME OF THIS GEM HERE
IS "LOVE."
-I AM THE FEELING OF LOVE.
-THE FEELING OF LOVE, IS IT?
-NO, KRAEHE, STOP!
-ALL YOU CHILDREN
WHO LOVE STORIES,
COME GATHER 'ROUND.
[ LAUGHS EVILLY ]