-ONCE UPON A TIME,
THERE WAS A MAN WHO DIED.
THE MAN TRIED TO KEEP SPINNING
HIS STORY EVEN AFTER HIS DEATH,
BUT THE STORY
JUST WOULDN'T MOVE ALONG.
FRUSTRATED,
THE MAN LOST HIS PATIENCE
AND CALLED A DUCK
INTO THE STORY.
THE LITTLE DUCK TRIED HER BEST
FOR THE PRINCE.
SHE TRANSCENDED
HER STANDING IN THE WORLD
AND CAME TO LOVE THE PRINCE.
HOWEVER, SHE WAS ONLY A DUCK.
SHE WAS FATED TO SOMEDAY
TURN INTO A SPECK OF LIGHT
AND VANISH.
YES, THAT WAS
THE TEAR-JERKING ENDING
THE STORY HAD DECIDED ON.
[ RITSUKO OKAZAKI'S
"MORNING GRACE" PLAYS ]
-[ SINGING IN JAPANESE ]
-AND SO,
THE PRINCE AND THE PRINCESS
LIVED HAPPILY EVER -- HAPPILY?
HAPPINESS IN THE STORIES
IS, AT MOST, A TRIFLING MATTER
OF A COUPLE OF LINES AT THE END,
THE EPITOME OF BOREDOM.
NO, SHOW ME
A MAGNIFICENT TRAGEDY --
A CATACLYSM OF TEARS FROM WHICH
NOT ONE OF THE PLAYERS IS SAVED
AND TO WHICH
A HAPPY ENDING NEVER COMES.
[ LAUGHS EVILLY ]
CONGRATULATIONS.
-PRINCE, WHAT DO YOU HOPE
TO DO AT THIS POINT?
DOES IT NOT MATTER TO YOU
WHAT HAPPENS TO THE GIRL
SINKING INTO DESPAIR
INSIDE OF ME?
-I WILL SAVE THE PRINCESS,
NO MATTER WHAT.
-QUACK!
-YOU MEAN TO TELL ME
IT'S YOUR INTENTION
TO TAKE A HUMAN GIRL RAISED
ON MY BLOOD AS YOUR PRINCESS?
-THAT'S RIGHT.
-MYTHO!
-MYTHO, ARE YOU --
-[ LAUGHS EVILLY ]
YOU FOOL!
[ CROWS CAWING ]
REMEMBER,
THOSE CROWS WERE ONCE PEOPLE.
WOULD YOU RAISE YOUR SWORD
AGAINST THEM, PRINCE?
[ CAWING CONTINUES ]
-WHAT WILL YOU DO, MYTHO?
-CROWS, DELIVER THE HEART
OF THE PRINCE UNTO ME.
-GIVE US YOUR HEART!
GIVE US YOUR HEART!
-CURSED RAVEN,
YOUR CRUELTY KNOWS NO END.
-GIVE US YOUR HEART!
GIVE US YOUR HEART!
-QUACK!
-GIVE US YOUR HEART!
GIVE US YOUR HEART!
-QUACK!
[ SCREAMING ]
-[ GASPS ]
-MYTHO!
-[ GRUNTING ]
-GIVE ME YOUR HEART!
-GIVE ME YOUR HEART! AAH! AAH!
-[ Echoing ] HEART!
-[ GROANS ]
-[ LAUGHS EVILLY ]
-GIVE US YOUR HEART!
GIVE US YOUR HEART!
-[ SIGHS ]
-GIVE US YOUR HEART!
GIVE US YOUR HEART!
-MYTHO!
-GIVE US YOUR HEART!
GIVE US YOUR HEART!
-STOP THIS NOW!
-GIVE US YOUR HEART!
GIVE US YOUR HEART!
-QUACK!
-DUCK, WHAT --
WHAT ARE YOU DOING?
-QUACK!
-GIVE US YOUR HEART!
GIVE US YOUR HEART!
-I SAID STOP!
-GIVE US YOUR HEART!
-WE HAVE TO HELP MYTHO!
-DUCK.
"THE DUCK FLAPPED
WITH ALL HER STRENGTH,
"HURRYING TO THE SIDE
OF THE PRINCE.
"AS IF IT HAD
SENSED HER FEELINGS,
A GUST OF WIND CAME TO HER AID."
-GIVE US YOUR HEART!
GIVE US YOUR HEART!
-STOP IT!
[ CROWS GASP ]
-QUACK?
-[ SCREAMING ]
-[ GASPS ]
-[ GROANS ]
[ CROWS CAWING ]
-QUACK!
-[ GASPS ]
[ CAWING CONTINUES ]
-[ GROANING ]
-"THE CROWS' RELENTLESS ATTACKS
ON THE DUCK...
"ST...ST...ST...
STILL KEPT GOING."
-[ GROANS ]
-[ GASPS ]
-DUCK!
-HEY! WAIT!
-[ GROANS ] MOVE IT!
I HAVE TO GO.
-AND WHAT WILL YOU DO?
YOU SAID YOURSELF
THAT YOU WERE USELESS
TO PROTECT ANYONE AS A KNIGHT.
YOU'LL JUST END UP
DYING IN VAIN.
ISN'T THAT RIGHT?
YOU DECIDED TO WRITE A STORY,
DIDN'T YOU?
THEN WRITE IT TO THE END.
CONCENTRATE.
ARE YOU LISTENING TO ME?
-DAMN IT.
-[ GASPS ]
SOMEONE'S COMING, ZURA.
-[ SIGHS ]
-WAIT. ISN'T THAT...?
[ CHAINS CLINKING ]
GET INSIDE.
-OH!
-QUACK.
-YOUR HEART!
YOUR HEART!
-QUACK! QUACK!
-YOUR HEART!
-QUACK!
PLEASE, STOP IT!
-YOUR HEART!
-[ Thinking ]
AT THIS RATE -- AT THIS RATE,
I'LL JUST BE LETTING THEM
STEAL MY HEART.
SO I REALLY HAVE NO CHOICE
AFTER ALL BUT TO SEAL HIM AWAY
BY RUNNING MY SWORD
THROUGH MY OWN HEART AGAIN?
-NO.
IT'S NOT LIKE THAT, MYTHO.
DAMN. IS IT TRUE THEN?
DO I REALLY NOT HAVE ENOUGH
POWER TO REWRITE THE STORY?
-BUT THAT DEPENDS ON --
I'M JUST A DUCK.
JUST A DUCK WITH NO POWER.
JUST A DUCK
WHO CAN'T DO ANYTHING.
-THAT'S RIGHT,
EVEN THOUGH YOU TRANSCENDED
YOUR DUCK'S PLACE IN THE WORLD
AND TRIED SO HARD.
BUT YOU SEE, UNFORTUNATELY,
THIS STORY WON'T HAVE
A HAPPY ENDING,
NO MATTER HOW HARD
YOU EXERT YOURSELF.
THE MORE YOU STRUGGLE,
THE MORE TRAGIC
IT WILL ULTIMATELY BECOME.
WHY, YOU ASK?
[ LAUGHS EVILLY ]
WHO OF US CAN TELL?
-I WILL NOT ALLOW YOU
TO LEAD THE STORY
DOWN A PATH TO TRAGEDY.
-FAKIR, ARE YOU JUST
GONNA GIVE UP?
-THAT'S IT.
THERE'S NO OTHER WAY NOW.
-WHAT -- WHAT CAN I DO?
-SINK INTO THE DEPTHS
OF ETERNAL DESPAIR
AS YOU VAINLY DREAM
OF A HAPPY ENDING TO THE STORY.
THE GREATEST TRAGEDY
HAS NO FINALE.
[ CROWS GASP, CAW ]
-[ WHIMPERS, GASPS ]
-HERE AND NOW, I WILL
PIERCE THIS HEART ONCE MORE.
-WHAT?
-THAT'S RIDICULOUS.
IF YOU SEAL ME AWAY,
THE PRINCESS WILL ALSO BE.
-NO MATTER HOW MANY YEARS
MAY PASS,
I VOW I WILL RETURN AGAIN
AND DEFEAT YOU.
ONCE THAT'S DONE, I WILL GO
AND END MY OWN LIFE
AND MEET THE PRINCESS IN HEAVEN.
-NO!
-YOU MEAN YOU'RE GOING
TO LOSE YOUR HEART
AND SUFFER THROUGH THAT
ALL OVER AGAIN?
-AFTER YOU FINALLY GOT
YOUR HEART BACK,
YOU MUSTN'T DO THAT.
YOU MUSTN'T.
YOU MUSTN'T!
-[ GASPS ]
-HMM?
-YOU MUSTN'T!
YOU MUSTN'T DO THAT!
MYTHO, PLEASE STOP!
DON'T GIVE UP!
-TUTU.
-DON'T GIVE UP!
-WELL, YOU STILL INTEND
TO RESIST THE FATE
YOU'VE BEEN GIVEN?
-FAKIR, I WANT
TO HELP MYTHO ONE MORE TIME.
-DUCK.
-WHAT'S THAT?
DO MY EARS DECEIVE ME?
A MERE DUCK HELP THE PRINCE?
HOW DELICIOUSLY FUTILE.
-TELL ME.
SINCE YOU ARE NO LONGER
PRINCESS TUTU,
WHAT EXACTLY
DO YOU INTEND TO DO?
-DON'T GIVE UP, EVERYONE.
DON'T LET THEM BEAT YOU.
LET'S GIVE THIS STORY
A HAPPY ENDING.
-THE DEPTHS OF DESPAIR --
I FEEL SO CALM HERE.
NO ONE TO TRICK ME,
NO ONE FOR ME TO RESENT.
THERE'S NOTHING HERE,
NOT EVEN LOVING.
I'LL JUST KEEP DANCING
UNTIL I DIE AWAY.
-[ LAUGHS EVILLY ] THANK YOU.
THE HUMAN GIRL WITH THE BLOOD
OF THE RAVEN FROM THE STORY,
YOUR TRAGEDY HAS LED
THE PERFECT TOUCH --
A LITTLE ADDED FLOURISH
TO MY TALE.
EVEN THOUGH
YOU'D REALIZE THE TOWN
WAS BEING CONTROLLED
BY MY STORY,
YOU STILL BELIEVE
THE RAVEN'S FALSE SCENARIO,
AND NOW HERE YOU ARE,
GETTING READY TO DIE AWAY
IN THE DEPTHS OF DESPAIR.
-[ CRIES ]
-WHAT?
I WOULD'VE THOUGHT YOU HAD
LONG LOST
THE CAPACITY FOR SORROW.
TRAGEDY UPON TRAGEDY.
WELL DONE.
YOU HAVE MY THANKS.
-I KNOW I'M JUST A DUCK.
AND I CAN'T EVEN
PUT ON TOE SHOES.
BUT I FEEL LIKE I CAN DANCE
FOR MYTHO AND RUE AND EVERYONE.
FAKIR, HELP ME.
-I'LL TRY, DUCK.
-DANCE WITH ME, EVERYONE.
[ RAVENS CAW ]
-[ GASPS ]
-PRINCE, SAVE THE PRINCESS.
-TUTU.
[ CHOIR VOCALIZING ]
-LET'S ALL DANCE TOGETHER
AND REMEMBER OUR TRUE SELVES.
-WHAT DO YOU THINK YOU CAN DO?
YOU'RE NOTHING BUT A DUCK.
[ TCHAIKOVSKY'S "WALTZ
OF THE FLOWERS" PLAYING ]
-THE REAL ME IS JUST A DUCK,
BUT I CAN STILL DANCE.
SO I SHOULD BE ABLE
TO COMMUNICATE
MY FEELINGS
THROUGH DANCING, TOO.
I WON'T SIT AND DO NOTHING
AND THEN DECIDE
I CAN'T DO ANYTHING
BECAUSE I'M THE ONE
WHO'S GONNA BE MAKING MY STORY.
LET'S ALL GO BACK TO THE REAL
SELVES INSIDE OUR OWN STORIES.
LET'S TREASURE OUR OWN FEELINGS,
NOT THE ONES THAT SOMEBODY ELSE
HAS CHOSEN FOR US.
[ "WALTZ OF THE FLOWERS"
CONTINUES ]
-IT WAS TRUE THAT HER DANCE
DID NOT POSSESS
THE GRACE AND BEAUTY
OF PRINCESS TUTU'S.
HOWEVER, IT WAS OVERFLOWING
WITH INTENSE, POWERFUL EMOTION
THAT SHONE A WARM LIGHT
ON THE HEARTS
OF ALL THE PEOPLE WHO SAW IT.
-A MERE DUCK.
IF YOU WANT TO DANCE THAT BADLY,
COME DANCE ALL YOU LIKE
IN THE DARKNESS OF DESPAIR.
-CURSED RAVEN! [ GRUNTS ]
-CROWS, DANCE WITH THE DUCK
UNTIL SHE EXHAUSTS HER STRENGTH
AND DIES.
[ LAUGHING EVILLY ]
[ CROWS CAWING ]
-QUACK!
-COME ON, DUCK.
-[ Thinking ] DUCK? I SEE.
SO HE CAN WRITE STORIES
IF THEY ARE ABOUT THAT GIRL.
[ CRASH ]
[ GASPS ]
-[ GASPS ]
-[ GRUNTING ]
-AAH! AAH!
[ GRUNTS ] QUACK!
QUACK.
AHH!
QUACK! QUACK!
-TUTU, I WON'T GIVE UP AGAIN.
I WILL SAVE RUE.
THAT'S ANOTHER REASON...
WHY I MUST KILL THE RAVEN.
-[ GROANING ]
-[ SCRIBBLING ]
-QUACK! AHH!
[ CROW CAWS ]
-WHY CAN'T -- WHY CAN'T I STOP
THESE CROWS FROM HURTING HER?
DAMN IT.
-[ GRUNTS ]
-[ GASPS ]
-[ PANTING ]
-QUACK!
-[ BREATHING HEAVILY ]
-DUCK!
-I FOUND YOU, YOU VILE
DESCENDANT OF REPUGNANT HANDS.
-WAIT! LET'S NOT GET VIOLENT.
-THE OTHER BOOKMEN HAVE TURNED
INTO CROWS, LEAVING ONLY ME.
WERE I TO CUT OFF YOUR HANDS,
IT WOULD NOT BE
PUNISHMENT ENOUGH.
-RUE, YOU MUST NOT GIVE IN
TO DESPAIR.
IF MY VOICE REACHES YOU...
-[ GROANS ]
[ CROWS CAWING ]
[ "WALTZ OF THE FLOWERS"
CONTINUES ]
-[ GROANS ] FAKIR IS JUST TRYING
TO END THE STORY.
-TELL HIM TO STOP.
LOOK AT THE TOWN FULL OF CROWS.
DON'T RESIST HIM ANYMORE
WITH YOUR IMMATURE ABILITIES.
THE STORY IS STILL BEING WRITTEN
BY A MIGHTY POWER.
ALL IMMATURE EFFORTS WILL DO
IS INVITE UNFORESEEN TRAGEDY.
-[ GASPS ]
-[ GROANING ]
I WON'T GIVE UP.
-COME ON, DUCK.
-FAKIR, I CAN STILL KEEP GOING.
I CAN STILL DANCE.
-ALL RIGHT THEN.
-[ GRUNTS ]
HYAH!
-LOOK OUT!
-[ GROANS ]
-[ GRUNTS ]
FAKIR, WRITE!
-FAKIR'S VOICE DISAPPEARED.
QUACK!
[ CROW CAWS ]
-QUACK!
-FAKIR?
QUACK!
-DUCK.
-FAKIR.
-DAMN IT.
-WHAT HAPPENED?
-WRITE. WRITE FOR THE PERSON
WHO'S WAITING FOR YOUR STORY.
-[ GASPS ]
DUCK.
-IT'S FAKIR'S VOICE.
FAKIR, I CAN STILL...
-"THE DUCK STOOD UP.
"NO MATTER HOW MUCH PAIN
SHE WAS SUFFERING,
"THE DUCK WOULD NOT
STOP HER DANCING.
"SHE WILLED HERSELF
TO KEEP DANCING
BECAUSE IT WAS THE ONLY THING
SHE COULD DO AS SHE WAS NOW."
-[ GASPS ] RUE!
[ "WALTZ OF THE FLOWERS"
CONTINUES ]
-DON'T GIVE IN
TO THE RAVEN'S BLOOD.
DON'T BE HELD CAPTIVE
BY DESPAIR.
LET'S GIVE THIS STORY
A HAPPY ENDING.
DON'T GIVE UP.
DON'T BE AFRAID.
[ GROANING ]
-"HER TINY BODY WAS SO WOUNDED
"THAT SHE COULDN'T EVEN
STAY ON HER FEET.
"AND YET, IN ORDER TO GUIDE
THE PRINCE AND EVERYBODY ELSE
"FROM DARK DESPAIR
TO A HAPPY ENDING,
"THE DUCK DANCED ON AND ON,
DISREGARDING THE PAIN,
NEVER LOSING HOPE."
[ CROWS CAW, SQUAWK ]
-"THE POWER FLOWED OUT FROM
DEEP WITHIN THE DUCK'S BODY,
UNQUENCHABLE AND INEXHAUSTIBLE."
-[ GASPS ] WHAT IS THAT?
IS THAT THE LIGHT?
THAT'S RIGHT.
IT'S THE LIGHT THAT ALWAYS
BURNED IN MY BREAST
WHEN I THOUGHT OF TUTU.
-"ONE BY ONE, THAT POWER
WARMED THE PEOPLE'S HEARTS,
"WHICH HAD BEEN FROZEN
BY THE RAVEN'S BLOOD.
"THAT POWER WAS...
-HOPE.
-[ GROWLS ]
-...HOPE."
-HOPE? THAT'S IMPOSSIBLE!
OHH! WHERE DID IT COME FROM?
-AND MY NAME
IS PRINCE SIEGFRIED.
I CALL THE NAME
OF THE PRINCESS, RUE!
-THE PRINCE'S VOICE?
I'M DOWN HERE.
-AH!
-WHAT?
[ GASPS ]
[ "WALTZ OF THE FLOWERS" STOPS ]
[ WINGS FLAPPING ]
-[ GASPS ]
-RUE, I'VE COME FOR YOU.
-MY PRINCE.
-LET'S DEFEAT THE RAVEN.
-[ GROWLS ]
[ "WALTZ OF THE FLOWERS"
RESUMES ]
-[ GASPS ]
-MYTHO, RUE.
-MYTHO.
[ GROANING, MOANING ]
-[ SIGHS ]
[ GROANING, MOANING CONTINUES ]
[ TWINKLE ]
-[ SIGHS ]
HERE WE GO.
[ PULSATING ]
-YES.
-THE STORY WILL END.
-AH!
-WHAT?! IT'S ENDING?
-[ SCREAMING ]
[ SCREAMING FADES ]
-[ GASPS ]
MYTHO! RUE!
I'M SO...GLAD.
-NO! DUCK! [ GASPS ]
[ TWINKLING ]
-HMM?
-HUH?
-[ MEOWS ]
-I KNOW
WHERE THE STORY IS, ZURA.
IT'S THIS WAY, ZURA.
I'M BACK, ZURA.
-WELCOME BACK
TO THE STORY, PRINCE.
THE ENTRANCE IS THIS WAY.
-AH!
-[ GASPS ]
-WHAT'S THIS? HERE, ZURA.
-I SEE.
EVERYTHING THAT HAPPENED
IN GOLD CROWN TOWN
THIS THING WAS RECORDING
AS A STORY --
A MECHANISM THAT GIVES BIRTH
TO THE TRAGEDY
DROSSELMEYER ENJOYS.
-TRAGEDY.
HUH?
-FAKIR, WHAT ARE YOU DOING?
-I WILL WRITE THE REST.
-WHAT?
-THE PRINCE CAN LIVE
FREELY AS HE PLEASES.
-AH.
RUE.
-YES?
-I WANT YOU TO COME WITH ME
INTO THE STORY AS MY PRINCESS.
-BUT I -- I HAVE THE RAVEN'S
BLOOD INSIDE OF ME.
-RAVEN'S BLOOD --
I WONDER IF IT'S STILL
RUNNING INSIDE MY VEINS AS WELL.
-PRINCE.
-FAKIR, ACCORDING TO THE STORY,
I'M SUPPOSED TO LOVE EVERYONE,
BUT -- BUT RIGHT NOW, I...
RIGHT NOW I SIMPLY WANT TO LOVE
RUE THE MOST OUT OF ANYONE.
-[ GASPS ]
[ CRIES ]
-RUE?
-IDIOT. WHAT'S WRONG WITH THAT?
-I'M SO GLAD.
-YOU'RE DUCK, AREN'T YOU?
-QUACK.
-I TRULY AM GLAD
I GOT TO MEET YOU.
THANK YOU.
-QUACK.
-I LOVE YOU, DUCK.
-I LOVE YOU, TOO, RUE.
[ CLASSICAL MUSIC PLAYING ]
[ BELL TOLLING ]
-AH! THIS IS LOVEY-DOVEY, ZURA.
[ TOLLING CONTINUES ]
-THANK YOU, TUTU, FAKIR.
-ONCE UPON A TIME,
THERE WAS A MAN WHO DIED.
THE FINAL STORY HE SPUN WAS
GOING TO BE A BRILLIANT TRAGEDY.
HOWEVER, THE STORY HAD
AN UNEXPECTED HAPPY ENDING,
AND IT WAS TRIGGERED BY ONE DUCK
THAT THE MAN HIMSELF
HAD CALLED INTO THE TALE.
[ BOTH LAUGH ]
-HUH?
-OH!
[ MUSIC CONTINUES ]
-COULD YOU PLEASE BE QUIET?!
[ CATS MEOWING ]
-TO THINK A MERE DUCK
HAD THAT MUCH HOPE.
MY BEAUTIFUL TRAGEDY IS RUINED.
I NEVER DREAMED
THE CHARACTERS INSIDE THE STORY
WOULD BE ABLE
TO CHANGE THE STORY THEMSELVES.
WAIT, WHAT IF IT HAPPENS
THAT ALL THIS TIME
I'VE BEEN A CHARACTER
IN SOMEONE'S STORY, TOO?
OH, WELL, EVEN IF I AM,
I'LL JUST DO WHAT I WANT.
HUH? OH, UZURA, YOU'RE HERE.
THIS STORY IS OVER.
YOU CAN'T STAY OVER THERE.
NOW, WHY DON'T WE GO
TO ANOTHER STORY?
-AH!
-THIS TIME,
ACTUALLY BE USEFUL TO ME.
-I DON'T GET IT, ZURA.
-[ LAUGHS ]
-AND THERE WAS ANOTHER MAN
WHO BEGAN WRITING A STORY.
THAT STORY, FULL OF HOPE,
HAS ONLY JUST BEGUN.