-ONCE UPON A TIME,
THERE WAS A PRINCESS
WHO WAS HELD CAPTIVE.
SHE WAS IMPRISONED
IN THE DEMON KING'S CASTLE,
HER FREEDOM TAKEN FROM HER.
THE PRINCESS HAD NO CHOICE
BUT TO DANCE LIKE A PUPPET
TO THE TUNE SET BY THE WHIMS
OF HER SADISTIC CAPTOR.
ONE DAY, A HERO
CAME TO FIGHT THE DEMON KING,
SEEKING TO SAVE THE PRINCESS.
HOWEVER, THERE WAS NO WAY THE
HERO COULD ATTAIN THE VICTORY.
FOR YOU SEE,
THE HERO DID NOT KNOW
THAT HE HIMSELF WAS A PUPPET
THAT THE DEMON KING HAD CREATED.
[ RITSUKO OKAZAKI'S
"MORNING GRACE" PLAYS ]
-[ SINGING IN JAPANESE ]
[ SINGING CONTINUES ]
[ TCHAIKOVSKY'S
"FINAL WALTZ AND APOTHEOSIS"
FROM "THE NUTCRACKER" PLAYS ]
-[ GASPS ] FAKIR!
-[ GASPS ] TUTU!
-WHERE AM I?
GEARS?
WHY ARE THEY ALL STOPPED?
WHAT AM I DOING IN A PLACE
LIKE THIS?
WHAT SHOULD I DO NOW?
FAKIR!
-[ GRUNTS ]
[ Thinking ] DROSSELMEYER --
THE MAN WHO TOYS
WITH EVERYONE'S FATES.
IS HE OUT THERE SOMEWHERE,
LAUGHING AS HE WATCHES HER
AND MYTHO SUFFER?
WHERE IS SHE RIGHT NOW?
IS SHE WHERE DROSSELMEYER IS?
WHERE THE HELL IS THAT?
-BY NOW, THE STORY
MAY HAVE PROGRESSED
TO THE POINT
WHERE WE CAN DO NOTHING.
IN THAT CASE,
THE ONLY ONE WHO CAN FIGHT
IS HE WHO CARRIES
THE SAME BLOOD.
-YOU MEAN I SHOULD WRITE, THEN?
THERE'S NO OTHER WAY
THAT I'LL BE ABLE
TO SAVE HER AT THIS POINT.
-WHERE IS THE EXIT?
I MUST LEAVE THIS PLACE.
I KNOW WHERE THEY ARE.
THE OTHER HEART SHARDS ARE IN
THE FIVE GATES AROUND THE TOWN.
I MUST RETURN THEM
TO MYTHO SOON.
AND THEN MYTHO WILL RETURN
TO THE STORY,
AND I'LL GO BACK
TO BEING...A DUCK.
[ WHIZ! ]
[ CLATTER! ]
WHAT'S THIS?
A PUPPET?
-YES! THAT'S RIGHT!
YOU'RE IN THE PUPPET WORLD NOW!
[ LAUGHS ]
-WHO'S THIS?
YOU'RE PRINCESS TUTU,
AREN'T YOU?
-[ CHUCKLES ] IT'S TUTU!
IT'S TUTU!
IT'S PRINCESS TUTU!
-I WONDER WHAT TUTU IS
DOING HERE?!
-DO YOU KNOW
WHERE THIS PLACE IS?
PLEASE TELL ME!
WHY WAS I BROUGHT HERE?
WAS THERE SOME REASON?
WHY HAS EVERYTHING IN THIS PLACE
JUST STOPPED?
-THAT'S RATHER IRRESPONSIBLE
OF YOU, WOULDN'T YOU SAY --
NOT KNOWING WHERE YOU ARE?
-THEN PLEASE! TELL ME!
-TUTU SAYS SHE WANTS US
TO TELL HER.
-PRINCESS TUTU IN A PICKLE!
-A PICKLE!
[ LAUGHTER ]
-ANSWER ME!
[ LAUGHTER STOPS ]
-YOU'RE THE ONE WHO STOPPED
EVERYTHING, PRINCESS TUTU.
DIDN'T YOU KNOW?
-THIS IS THE INSIDE
OF THE STORY.
-AND YOU ARE THE ONE
WHO CAUSED THE STORY TO STOP.
-CAUSED THE STORY TO STOP?
I DID IT?
-THAT'S RIGHT!
TUTU STOPPED THE STORY!
-TUTU STOPPED ALL THE GEARS!
SHE STOPPED THEM!
TUTU STOPPED THEM!
-STOP IT!
[ GASPS ]
MY BODY!
IT WON'T MOVE!
-[ Thinking ] HEAR THE VOICE
WHICH IS VOICELESS
AND SEE THE SHAPE
WHICH IS SHAPELESS.
WHAT AM I SUPPOSED
TO DO WITH THAT?
WHAT SHOULD I WRITE?
[ STRAINING ]
[ GRUNTS ]
[ BREATHING HEAVILY ]
DAMN IT!
I HAVE TO WRITE!
I HAVE TO WRITE.
[ PANTING ]
-[ GROANS ]
WHERE IS THE HEART?
DAUGHTER, HURRY UP AND FETCH ME
A HEART.
-DEAR FATHER,
NOW THAT I HAVE GONE
AND DYED THE PRINCE'S HEART
IN YOUR BLOOD,
HE'LL DEFINITELY BECOME
MINE, RIGHT, FATHER?
-ARE YOU SAYING YOU CANNOT TRUST
WHAT I TELL YOU?
-OH, NO! OF COURSE NOT!
-AND TO THINK ON TOP OF THAT,
YOU ONLY CONSIDER YOURSELF
AND NOT ME, YOUR FATHER.
-THAT'S NOT TRUE!
I LOVE YOU, FATHER, BUT --
-IT'S ONLY NATURAL FOR
A DAUGHTER TO LOVE HER FATHER!
[ RUMBLE! ]
YOU'RE PATHETIC.
TO THINK YOU CAN'T EVEN
GET THE LOVE OF THE PRINCE
IN THE STORY.
AT THIS POINT,
YOU NO LONGER HAVE ANY VALUE
TO ME AS A DAUGHTER.
-[ GASPS ] FATHER!
-YOU SHOULD AT LEAST
GIVE ME YOUR HEART
SO THAT I MIGHT BE RESTORED
TO SOME DEGREE, HOWEVER SMALL.
-FATHER! [ WHIMPERS ]
FORGIVE ME! I'M SORRY!
-I HAVE NOT GIVEN YOU LEAVE,
KRAEHE!
-HAVE I...TURNED INTO A PUPPET?
DID I DO SOMETHING BAD,
IS THAT WHY?
[ TAPPING ]
[ GASPS ]
IS THAT...?
UZURA!
-OH!
I FOUND TUTU, ZURA!
-WHAT ARE YOU DOING HERE, UZURA?
-I FOLLOWED YOU, ZURA!
WHAT ARE YOU DOING, ZURA?
-I THINK I'VE SOMEHOW
TURNED INTO A PUPPET.
-A PUPPET, ZURA?
-UH, IT'S NOT THAT
I DON'T LIKE BEING A PUPPET.
IT'S JUST --
-OOH!
-UZURA?
-OOH, OOH.
PUPPETS, ZURA?
[ SCREAMS ]
-UZURA!
-JETé ENTRELACé.
-[ GASPS ]
MY FEET ARE MOVING ON THEIR OWN!
-FOUETTé ROND DE JAMBE
EN TOURNANT.
-MR. DROSSELMEYER?
IS THIS THE WORLD
WHERE MR. DROSSELMEYER IS?
HOW? WHY?
I'M JUST A MARIONETTE
DANCING EXACTLY AS I'M TOLD.
I DON'T LIKE THIS.
I WANT TO DANCE MORE --
MORE FREELY!
-SUCH THINKING IS MISTAKEN.
MARIONETTES ARE
AT THEIR MOST FREE
WHEN THEY'RE BEING MANIPULATED
BY THEIR STRINGS.
YOU WON'T BE ABLE
TO LEAVE THIS PLACE
UNLESS YOU ACKNOWLEDGE THAT.
[ LAUGHS ]
-WHAT'S A PUPPET, ZURA?
-WELL, HER NAME IS UZURA.
BUT KARON -- HE MADE HER
FROM THE WOOD FROM EDEL
THAT DIDN'T BURN UP.
-FROM MISS EDEL?
-DOES THAT MEAN
I'M NOT UZURA, ZURA?
HUH?
OH!
[ FOOTSTEPS ]
[ GASPS ]
WHAT'S THIS, ZURA?
[ CLANKING ]
OH, IT TURNS, ZURA!
[ CLANKS ]
OOH!
[ BIRD CAWING ]
-CAW CAW. [ LAUGHS ]
[ DOOR OPENS ]
[ DOOR CLOSES ]
HELLO, KRAEHE.
COME HERE, WON'T YOU?
[ LAUGHS ]
-[ BREATHING HEAVILY ]
-MY PRINCE --
-COME, COME, NOW.
WHY THE HAUNTED LOOK?
LET'S ENJOY OURSELVES.
I WANT TO GET
THE ALL MY FEELINGS BACK --
THE SOONER, THE BETTER.
ONCE THAT'S TAKEN CARE OF,
I CAN GIVE THE RAVEN MY HEART.
-[ GASPS ]
WHAT ARE YOU SAYING?
THAT'S A JOKE, RIGHT?
THE PRINCE IS FATED
TO MARRY NO ONE BUT ME.
-MARRY YOU?
YOU, WHO IN SPITE
OF BEING A CROW,
HAVE THAT UGLY HUMAN BODY?
THAT'S THE JOKE.
THE ONLY THING THAT YOU
ARE ALLOWED TO DO IS LOVE ME.
-[ GASPS ]
-THE MOMENT YOU DYED MY HEART
WITH RAVEN'S BLOOD,
OUR FATES
WERE IMMEDIATELY SEALED.
-[ Thinking ] BUT I DID JUST
WHAT FATHER TOLD ME TO.
THEN I -- THEN I'D RATHER JUST
TAKE HIS HEART OUT AGAIN.
BUT I DON'T HAVE
THE PRINCE'S SWORD.
IF I THRUST THIS SWORD
INTO THE PRINCE, HE MIGHT DIE.
THAT'S FINE.
IF THAT HAPPENS, I, TOO, WILL --
[ BREATHING SHAKILY ]
-I HAVE ONE LAST FAVOR TO ASK --
AFTER YOU'VE RIPPED OUT
MY HEART,
I WANT YOU TO KISS IT
AND DYE YOUR LIPS CRIMSON
WITH MY BLOOD.
-[ GASPS ]
-WHAT'S THE MATTER?
CAN'T YOU DO IT?
[ LAUGHS ]
-WELL, LOOKS LIKE YOU'VE REACHED
YOUR LIMIT.
I'LL ADMIT, PICKING
DROSSELMEYER'S GRAVE TO WRITE AT
WAS PRETTY SHARP -- FOR YOU.
BUT IF THE WORDS
YOU SHOULD BE WRITING
AREN'T COMING TO YOU WITHOUT
YOU EVEN HAVING TO THINK --
-COULD YOU PLEASE BE
A LITTLE QUIETER?
-AND TO THINK, AT THIS MOMENT,
I HAVE VOLUMES UPON VOLUMES
THAT I WANT TO WRITE.
IT'S IRONIC.
-FASTER!
I'VE GOT TO WRITE FASTER!
-GOOD GRIEF!
YOU'D BE BETTER OFF
LETTING THE STORY
PULL YOU ALONG LIKE A GOOD BOY.
WELL,
IT'S OF NO REAL CONSEQUENCE.
YOU NEEDN'T FRET, LITTLE DUCK.
I'LL BE COMING FOR YOU SOON.
[ TCHAIKOVSKY'S "MARCH"
FROM "THE NUTCRACKER" PLAYS ]
[ BIRD CAWING ]
[ RUSTLING ]
-[ LAUGHING ]
[ GRUNTS ]
[ ALL CAWING ]
[ GIGGLING ]
-[ GASPS ]
[ DRINK POURING ]
WHO'S THERE?
-WELCOME TO THIS QUAINT,
LITTLE GAP IN TIME,
MY DEAR PRINCESS TUTU.
-MR. DROSSELMEYER!
SO, WHAT DID THOSE PUPPETS MEAN
WHEN THEY TOLD ME
I STOPPED THE STORY?
I'M JUST...[Straining]
...TRYING MY BEST
TO COMPLETELY RETURN
THE PRINCE'S HEART TO HIM.
-TELL ME, HAVE YOU DISCOVERED
ALL THE LOCATIONS
OF THE SCATTERED HEART SHARDS?
-WHAT? UM, I'M NOT QUITE SURE,
BUT I THINK THAT THEY'RE HIDDEN
IN THE FIVE GATES AROUND THE T--
-MY CONGRATULATIONS TO YOU.
-WHAT?
SO, IF I RETURN THOSE
FIVE SHARDS TO HIM,
THE PRINCE WILL GO BACK
TO NORMAL AND DEFEAT THE RAVEN
AND THEN --
-NO, NO, NO.
THAT WOULD BE HOPELESSLY BORING!
YOU'RE A STORY CHARACTER.
YOU CAN DO BETTER THAN THAT!
-CHARACTER?
BUT HOW CAN THAT BE?
I'M REALLY ONLY A DUCK.
-CORRECT, BUT YOU'RE
INSIDE THE STORY RIGHT NOW.
EVERYBODY IS.
TAKE A LOOK.
-[ GASPS ] HUH?
[ CLANK! ]
RUE.
FAKIR.
MYTHO!
-EVERYONE'S SUFFERING, YOU SEE.
THIS IS THE WAY IT HAS TO BE.
TUTU HAS SOMETHING
SHE SHOULD SUFFER OVER, TOO --
THE CHOICE TO CONFESS HER LOVE
AND IMMEDIATELY VANISH,
OR NEVER TO CONFESS HER LOVE
AND, THEREBY,
FOREVER LOSE THE PRINCE.
-NEVER MIND THAT. I --
-AND YET, TO THINK
RETURNING THE PRINCE TO NORMAL
IS MORE IMPORTANT TO YOU
THAN YOUR OWN PROBLEMS.
YOU'RE A MUCH DIFFERENT DUCK NOW
THAN THE ONE YOU ONCE WERE,
WHOSE SOLE DESIRE
WAS FOR THE PRINCE!
YOU SHOULD BE DESPERATELY
IN LOVE WITH THE PRINCE
AND WANT TO MARRY HIM!
AM I WRONG?
-I JUST...
-THAT'S RIGHT!
YOU SHOULDN'T FIGHT
WHAT'S NATURAL.
IT'S ONLY NATURAL TO WANT
TO MAKE THE PRINCE YOURS,
AND YOURS ALONE.
THERE'S NOTHING
TO BE ASHAMED OF.
I KNOW.
HOW DOES THIS IDEA
APPEAL TO YOUR NATURE?
SIMPLY PRETEND
YOU HAVEN'T REALIZED
THAT THE REMAINING HEART SHARDS
ARE HIDDEN IN THE FIVE GATES.
-WHAT?
-AFTER ALL,
NOBODY ELSE HAS REALIZED,
SO IF YOU DO THAT,
THERE WILL BE NOTHING
TO PART YOU FROM THE PRINCE.
-BUT --
-MY DEAR DUCK,
IF YOU CAN'T THINK
AT LEAST ON THAT LEVEL,
YOU'LL NEVER LEAVE HERE,
AND THE STORY
WILL STAY STOPPED, TOO.
[ GASPS ]
-[ GASPS ]
-WHAT'S THIS?
TUTU IS HERE,
AND YET THE GEARS ARE MOVING?
WHAT IS GOING ON?
OOH.
INTERESTING!
THE GEARS ARE STARTING
TO TURN BACKWARDS.
THE STORY WILL NOW
DOUBLE BACK ON ITSELF!
-WHAT?
-WHOA! WHOA!
-I NEVER ONCE
ENVISIONED SOMETHING LIKE THIS!
HOW INTRIGUING!
I WONDER WHAT WILL HAPPEN.
[ LAUGHS EVILLY ]
-I DON'T UNDERSTAND ANYMORE.
I BELIEVED THAT MY MARRIAGE
TO THE PRINCE
WAS THE FATE
THE STORY HAD DECIDED FOR US.
WAS I WRONG?
WHAT SHOULD I BELIEVE?
WHOM SHOULD I BELIEVE?
[ SOBBING ]
I WANT TO GO BACK TO THAT TIME
BEFORE I REMEMBERED EVERYTHING,
THAT TIME WHEN I WAS RUE!
[ BELL TOLLING ]
-HELP ME!
[ TOLLING CONTINUES ]
[ CRYING ]
I'M SORRY, FATHER!
DON'T TAKE MY HEART! FORGIVE ME!
[ CRYING ]
-THAT WAS...
-I'LL BE A GOOD GIRL!
-[ GASPS ]
-[ GRUNTS ]
-GET BEHIND ME.
-[ WHIMPERS ]
[ BIRD CAWING ]
-THAT'S THE PRINCE
BACK WHEN I FIRST MET HIM.
-YOU DON'T HAVE
TO WORRY ANYMORE.
[ GROANS ]
-D-DOES IT HURT?
-[ LIGHTLY GROANING ]
-I-I BROUGHT WATER.
-[ LIGHTLY GROANS ]
-[ GASPS ]
-THANK YOU.
-I HAVE TO GO.
-GO WHERE?
-BACK HOME TO MY FATHER.
-WHO ARE YOU?
-MY NAME IS...
-MY PITIFUL DAUGHTER,
WHO DESPITE BEING A CROW,
HAS BEEN BORN
INTO AN UGLY HUMAN BODY.
-I'M -- I'M NOT A CROW!
I'M A -- A PERSON!
I'M K-- RAE, REE, RU -- RUE.
MY NAME IS RUE!
CAN I COME SEE YOU AGAIN?
-YES.
-GOODBYE!
[ GEARS CLANKING ]
-WHAT'S GOING ON!?
-THE STORY IS FLOWING BACKWARDS!
-WHAT!?
-STOP IT! HURRY!
STOP IT WITH YOUR PEN! FAKIR!
-[ Thinking ]
THE STORY'S DOUBLING BACK?
[ GEARS CLANKING ]
-I'VE EXPERIENCED
A LOT OF NEW FEELINGS
SINCE BECOMING A HUMAN GIRL.
IN THE BEGINNING,
I DIDN'T THINK MY FEELINGS
FOR MYTHO WOULD GROW SO MUCH.
-I WILL NEVER GO BACK --
NOT TO THAT TIME
WHEN I CLUNG TO MY SWORD
AND SAID NOTHING BUT WORDS THAT
DEPRIVED MYTHO OF HIS FREEDOM!
-ALL OF MY FEELINGS
BELONG TO ME.
ALL FEELINGS ARE PRECIOUS
TO WHOM THEY BELONG.
AND I AM NOBODY'S MARIONETTE.
-I WILL NO LONGER COWARD
BEFORE FATE!
-WHATEVER IT TAKES!
-WE'LL GUARD HIM!
-TOGETHER!
[ UP-TEMPO CLASSICAL MUSIC
PLAYING ]
-[ GASPS ]
JUST NOW, I HEARD HER VOICE!
THAT'S RIGHT.
SHE'S CHANGED ME.
I CAN WRITE!
I CAN WRITE A STORY ABOUT HER!
B-BUT WAIT, THESE WORDS --
THEY'RE NOT MY WORDS.
WHAT ARE THEY?
[ GEARS CLANK ]
-OH!
EVERYTHING STOP MOVING, ZURA!
-THE STORY DOESN'T WANT
TO GO BACK ANY MORE THAN THAT.
-WHO'S THAT, ZURA?
UH, OH! ARE YOU A PUPPET, ZURA?
-I AM A PUPPET.
AND I AM YOU.
YOU ARE ALSO ME.
-I'M NOT UZURA, ZURA?
-I AM A PUPPET
WHO COULD NOT HAVE A HEART.
BUT YOU...
-OOOH.
[ DRIP! ]
[ GASPS ]
AHH.
-NOW, GO BACK TO WHERE DUCK IS.
-WAIT, ZURA!
-THESE ARE...ALL HER FEELINGS.
-I WANT TO GO BACK.
I WANT TO GO BACK
AND HELP MYTHO!
I WANT TO LEAVE THIS PLACE!
-HER FEELINGS FOR MYTHO
ARE SPILLING UP THROUGH MY HAND
AND OUT ONTO THE PAGE.
"IN THAT TIME,
"THE KNIGHT WHO HAD CAST AWAY
HIS SWORD CALLED HER NAME
IN ORDER TO LEAD HER
OUT OF THE DARKNESS!"
DU-U-U-U-U-CK!
-[ GASPS ]
FAKIR!
-THERE. GO ON!
-OH!
WHOA!
-[ GASPS ]
DUCK!
-FAKIR!
DID YOU WRITE A STORY ABOUT ME,
THEN?
-YEAH.
-THANK YOU.
-WHAT IS THIS?
FOR HER TO LEAVE HERE
WITHOUT MY PERMISSION?
SHE'S NOT TO BE UNDERESTIMATED.
AND THANKS TO THIS,
THE STORY IS STILL STOPPED.
[ GEARS CLANK ]
HM?
OH.
IT WOULD APPEAR THAT THERE IS
ONE WHO IS STILL DOUBLING BACK.
YOU'RE GOING TO FIND OUT
SOMETHING YOU WISH YOU HADN'T.
-NOW WHERE...AM I?
-WHAT'S WRONG?
-MY DAUGHTER'S BEEN KIDNAPPED
BY THE CROWS!
-WHAT? WE'LL START
SEARCHING OVER THERE!
-THANK YOU.
-[ CRYING ]
-THAT THERE -- THAT'S ME?
THE MAN....
AFTER ALL THIS,
I'M NOT THE RAVEN'S DAUGHTER?
I HAD A MOTHER.
I HAD A FATHER.
I'M A NORMAL HUMAN BEING?
-[ CAWS ]
-[ LAUGHS ]
WHAT A WRETCHED FATE.
-[ GASPS ]
AAAAH!
[ SCREAMING ]
-HM?
THE STORY'S
FINALLY STARTED MOVING.
MY, MY.
THANK GOODNESS, THANK GOODNESS.
-OOH, SO THAT MEANS
I'M NOT UZURA, ZURA?
MY HEART ISN'T LOVEY-DOVEY,
ZURA?
UH, OH.
WHERE AM I, ZURA?
AHH.
AAAH-AAAAAH.
I'M UP HIGH, ZURA!
[ RITSUKO OKAZAKI'S "THOUGH
MY LOVE IS SMALL" PLAYS ]
-[ SINGING IN JAPANESE ]
-MY LOVE HAS DONE NOTHING
BUT MAKE YOU INTO THIS.
I HAVE NO RIGHT TO LOVE YOU.
-DUCK DOESN'T KNOW.
THERE'S A THING
SHE DOESN'T KNOW.
-JUST NOW,
I WAS AFRAID OF MYTHO.
-EVEN IF I PUT WATER ON YOU,
YOU WON'T CHANGE BACK, ZURA?
-THAT'S WHY I'M ASKING
FOR YOUR HELP, AUTOR.
-SO THIS IS THE RAVEN.
-THIS FRAIL, EARNEST LOVE --
I MUST PROTECT THIS LOVE.
-ALL YOU CHILDREN WHO LOVE
STORIES, COME GATHER 'ROUND.
[ LAUGHS EVILLY ]