-ONCE UPON A TIME...
THERE WAS A MAN WHO DIED.
THE MAN HAD THE POWER
TO MAKE STORIES COME TRUE.
SO, HIS HANDS WERE CUT OFF
BY THE PEOPLE,
WHO WERE AFRAID
OF TRAGEDIES BECOMING REALITY.
WHEN THE MAN DIED, THE PEOPLE
HEAVED A GREAT SIGH OF RELIEF.
AS IT TURNED OUT, HOWEVER,
WHEN HIS HANDS WERE CUT OFF,
THE MAN HAD BEEN WRITING A STORY
IN HIS OWN BLOOD.
THAT WAS A STORY
HE COULD CONTINUE SPINNING
EVEN AFTER HE DIED --
A STORY OF THE MAN HIMSELF.
[ RITSUKO OKAZAKI'S
"MORNING GRACE" PLAYS ]
-[ SINGING IN JAPANESE ]
[ SINGING CONTINUES ]
-[ GASPS ]
[ COGS RATTLING ]
[ GASPS ]
WHAT?
THIS CAN'T BE!
TO THINK THE WORDS OF TRUE LOVE
TUTU WAS SUPPOSED TO SAY
PRINCESS KRAEHE ENDED UP SAYING
INSTEAD.
EVEN THOUGH SHE WAS RAISED
ON RAVEN'S BLOOD
AND SHOULDN'T EVEN KNOW
HOW TO LOVE.
[ LAUGHS ]
REGARDLESS, YOU STILL WILL BE
UNABLE TO ESCAPE TRAGEDY,
MY DEAR LITTLE DUCK.
[ LAUGHS EVILLY ]
-ARE -- ARE YOU GLAD TO HAVE IT,
PRINCE?
-I DON'T KNOW.
-SAY, UH...
I HAVE ANOTHER QUESTION.
DO YOU THINK YOU'LL LOVE ME?
-I DON'T KNOW.
-WELL, JUST TELL ME YOU LOVE ME.
-I LOVE YOU.
-I WANT TO HEAR YOU SAY
THAT YOU LOVE ME.
TRUST ME, MYTHO, YOU DO LOVE.
[ Crying ] PLEASE, I LOVE YOU!
MY PRINCE!
I HAVE EVER SINCE I WAS LITTLE!
I'VE ALWAYS LOVED YOU!
[ WIND HOWLING ]
-RUE.
-HE TOOK RUE.
YOU MONSTER!
-RELAX.
I HAVEN'T KILLED HER YET.
SHE'S DEEP IN MY STOMACH.
I SHOULD'VE DONE THIS
IN THAT FIGHT LONG AGO
AND SAVED US ALL THE TROUBLE.
SHE'S JUST A HUMAN GIRL I
KIDNAPPED ON A WHIM AND RAISED,
BUT SHE'S BEEN QUITE USEFUL.
IF YOU KILL ME,
YOU'LL BE KILLING
THE GIRL WITHIN ME, AS WELL.
LIKEWISE, IF YOU SING ME AWAY.
YOU HAVE NO CHOICE BUT
TO OFFER UP YOUR HEART TO ME.
-I CAN'T FIGHT, EVEN IF I RETURN
THE LAST HEART SHARD.
HOW HORRIBLE!
-PRINCE, I DEMAND YOU GIVE ME
YOUR HEART AT ONCE.
[ LAUGHS EVILLY ]
STILL RESISTING?
YOU MEAN TO IMPLY YOU STILL HAVE
SOME CHANCE OF SUCCESS, PRINCE?
-PRINCESS TUTU.
-YES?
-I WOULD LIKE FOR YOU TO RETURN
MY FINAL HEART SHARD.
-WHAT?
-HMM.
-PLEASE GIVE IT TO ME.
I HAVE TO SAVE HER.
NO, I-I WANT TO...SAVE RUE.
EXCRUCIATING PAIN
OF HAVING RAVEN'S BLOOD EAT AT
YOUR HEART -- I KNOW THAT PAIN.
IT STARTS IN THE WEAK PLACES
IN YOUR HEART
AND SPREADS RUTHLESSLY.
YOU CAN'T EVEN STOP YOURSELF
FROM HURTING THE PEOPLE
WHO ARE IMPORTANT TO YOU.
RUE HAS STOOD UP UNDER
THE BURDEN OF THAT SUFFERING
ALL ALONE
EVER SINCE SHE WAS SMALL.
HER LOVE WAS FRAIL, AND SHE WAS
ALWAYS AFRAID OF LOSING LOVE.
THE MORE SHE LOVED,
THE MORE SHE SUFFERED,
BUT THERE WAS NO ONE
SHE COULD EVEN SEEK HELP FROM.
BUT SHE NEVER THOUGHT
TO STOP LOVING.
WITH WORDS OF TRUE LOVE, SHE LED
ME OUT OF THE RAVEN'S DARKNESS.
IT'S MY TURN TO PROTECT HER NOW,
AND, IF POSSIBLE, I'D LIKE
TO TAKE RUE AS MY PRINCESS.
SO, PRINCESS TUTU...PLEASE
GIVE ME THE LAST HEART SHARD.
-YES.
[ CLASP CLICKS ]
-THANK YOU.
-AH, YES.
IF YOUR HEART IS NOT COMPLETE,
I CANNOT GAIN ETERNAL LIFE
FROM IT.
I ALMOST RUSHED THINGS
IN MY EAGERNESS.
-WHAT?
[ WHIMPERS ]
-WHAT'S THE MATTER?
-THE PENDANT WON'T COME OFF.
WHAT'S GOING ON?
WHY WON'T IT?
-[ GROWLING ]
-[ GASPS ]
-PRINCESS TUTU,
I GRANT YOU UNTIL DAWN.
YOU MUST GIVE THE FINAL SHARD
BACK TO THE PRINCE BY THEN.
-AAAH!
-[ SHRIEKS ]
PRINCE!
-IF YOU FAIL TO DO THIS,
I WILL TEAR THE PRINCE'S HEART
INTO PIECES.
-THIS TEA IS THE BLEND
THAT DROSSELMEYER LIKED TO DRINK
WHILE HE WAS WORKING.
HE USED THREE PARTS DARJEELING
AND THEN ADDED ASSAM.
[ FOOTSTEPS ]
[ HUFFS ]
TELL ME AGAIN
WHY I MUST DO THIS.
[ CAWING ]
IT CERTAINLY IS NOISY.
[ GASPS ]
[ CAWING CONTINUES ]
WH-WHAT'S GOING ON?!
-WHAT?
-BATHE IN HIS NOBLE BLOOD!
ALL PEOPLE WILL BECOME CROWS!
NOW CELEBRATE
MY TRIUMPHANT RETURN!
-PIKE AND LILIE?
[ CAWING CONTINUES ]
MR. CAT?
-YOU'D BETTER HURRY.
YOU HAVEN'T MUCH TIME, TUTU.
-[ GASPS ]
[ CRYING ]
-HUH?
[ SPARKLE! ]
-[ STRAINING ]
[ PANTS ]
I CAN'T TAKE IT OFF.
WHY NOT?!
-I WONDER.
-[ GASPS ]
-THIS IS BAD! FA--
-AUTOR, I'M BEGGING YOU. WOULD
YOU PLEASE BE A LITTLE QUI--
[ GASPS ]
-WELL, WELL...
THAT PERSON WRITING AT THAT DESK
LOOKS A LOT LIKE ME
WHEN I WAS YOUNGER.
COULD IT BE?
NO, I'M MISTAKEN.
I WOULD NEVER WAVER
ABOUT WRITING.
[ LAUGHS ]
-SO, YOU'RE DROSSELMEYER.
-HMM. THESE THINGS ALL LOOK
A LOT LIKE WHAT I USED,
BUT MOST OF THEM
APPEAR TO BE FAKES.
YOU'RE TRYING TO BE RESPONSIBLE
ABOUT YOUR WRITING, AREN'T YOU?
WELL, THAT'S WHY
YOU CAN'T WRITE.
YOU HAVE TO UNDERSTAND THAT
WHEN YOU'RE WRITING STORIES,
YOU SHOULD DO IT MORE FREELY
AND IRRESPONSIBLY.
JUST FOLLOW YOUR OWN FEELINGS.
-I HAVE NO DESIRE TO BECOME
LIKE YOU --
A DEMENTED, SADISTIC FOSSIL
WHO TOYS WITH PEOPLE'S FATES
FOR A LARK.
-THAT THINKING
WON'T GET US ANYWHERE.
-[ GASPS ]
MYTHO.
-THE RAVEN HAS REVIVED,
AND ALL OF THE PRINCE'S HEART
IS RETURNED TO HIM,
EXCEPT FOR THE SHARD
IN PRINCESS TUTU'S PENDANT.
-WHAT?
-BUT PRINCESS TUTU
CAN'T GIVE BACK THE PENDANT.
SO RIGHT NOW SHE'S SUFFERING.
-[ GRUNTS ]
WHAT?
MY HAND'S WRITING BY ITSELF.
-[ LAUGHS ]
YOU SEE, YOU HAVE MY BLOOD
RUNNING THROUGH YOUR VEINS.
-[ GRUNTS ]
-THAT WAS THE LAKE
CALLED DESPAIR.
IT WAS DARK AND DEEP,
JUST LIKE A DUCK'S EYES.
-WHAT ARE YOU INTENDING
TO MAKE ME WRITE?
-THE SORROWFUL, YET BEAUTIFUL
STORY OF LITTLE DUCK.
-THE STORY OF DUCK?
-AT THAT MOMENT,
DUCK COULD HEAR A VOICE.
IT WAS THE VOICE
OF DROSSELMEYER,
THE MAN
WHO CONTROLLED THE STORY.
-DUCK!
-IT'S BECAUSE YOU'RE SCARED
TO LET GO OF BEING PRINCESS TUTU
THAT YOU CAN'T GIVE BACK
THE HEART SHARD, RIGHT?
-NO! THAT'S NOT IT!
-YOU'RE AFRAID
TO PART WITH THE PRINCE.
-I JUST WANT --
-RUE WOULD BE CARVED INTO
THE PRINCE'S HEART FOR ETERNITY
BECAUSE SHE GAVE HERSELF OVER
TO THE RAVEN.
AND BY KEEPING THE HEART SHARD,
DUCK WOULD LIVE ON
IN THE PRINCE'S HEART
AS PRINCESS TUTU AND
NOT AS AN UGLY, LITTLE DUCK.
-IS IT...
IS IT ALL MY FAULT?
-YES, IT IS.
AND IN ORDER
TO TAKE OFF THE PENDANT,
YOU'LL HAVE TO LAY DOWN
YOUR LIFE.
DUCK BEGAN TO SINK
INTO THE LAKE OF DESPAIR,
WALKING FURTHER AND FURTHER IN.
-STOP IT!
DON'T GO, DUCK!
-DEEPER AND DEEPER.
-STOP IT!
[ GROANING ]
DUCK! [ GROANS ]
[ THUMP! ]
-KIR!
THERE ARE CROWS ALL OVER TOWN!
-[ BREATHING HEAVILY ]
D-DUCK...
-DUCK?
WHERE DID YOU GO, ZURA?
DUCK!
[ DRUMMING ]
-I GOT TO FIND --
-DON'T GO OUT THERE!
IT'S DANGEROUS!
-WHAT?
-NEVER MIND THAT.
WHAT HAPPENED TO YOUR HAND?
AND WHEN DID YOU WRITE A STORY?
WHAT HAPPENED?
TELL ME!
-DROSSELMEYER CAME, AND HE --
-DROSSELMEYER?
-BASTARD MADE ME WRITE
THE STORY.
-YOU MEAN DROSSELMEYER WAS HERE
IN THIS ROOM?
-YES.
-MAGNIFICENT!
[ GRUNTS ]
WHA-- WHAT'S WRONG?
-NOTHING.
-HEY, WHERE ARE YOU GOING?
HEY, WAIT!
[ CAWING ]
-WHAT'S GOING ON?
-IT -- IT LOOKS EXACTLY LIKE
THE CROW FESTIVAL SCENE
THAT TOOK PLACE
IN "THE PRINCE AND THE RAVEN."
[ CAWING CONTINUES ]
-SO THE RAVEN HAS CURSED THEM.
DAMN IT!
-HEY!
THE RAVEN'S CURSE, IS IT?
I WONDER
IF SHE'S ALL RIGHT, THEN.
-[ Thinking ]
THE LAKE OF DESPAIR.
WHERE IS THAT?
-THERE YOU ARE, ZURA.
-UZURA?
-DUCK JUST DISAPPEARED, ZURA.
-SO, YOU WERE WITH HER
WHEN IT HAPPENED?
WHERE IS SHE?
-THIS WAY, ZURA.
-I'M SORRY.
I'M SORRY, RUE.
I'M SORRY, MYTHO.
IF I VANISH...
THE HEART SHARD
WILL RETURN TO YOU.
[ DRUMMING ]
-THIS WAY, ZURA.
-[ Thinking ] WHAT?
OUTSIDE THE GATE?
I'VE NEVER EVEN THOUGHT
OF LEAVING THIS CITY.
NOW I SEE.
I WAS BEING CONTROLLED
BY DROSSELMEYER'S STORY.
THAT'S WHY.
LOOKS LIKE THE STORY STARTED
TO SPREAD BEYOND THE CITY WALLS.
-WHAT ARE YOU WAITING FOR, ZURA?
-OH, SORRY.
-HURRY UP, ZURA.
-[ GRUNTS ]
-HERE, ZURA.
-DUCK?
WHAT'S WITH THIS LAKE?
FOR SOME REASON, I CAN BREATHE.
IS THIS JUST ANOTHER STAGED
SETTING DROSSELMEYER PREPARED?
-[ Thinking ] I THOUGHT I WAS
DOING MY BEST FOR MYTHO'S SAKE.
BUT WAS IT FOR MY OWN SAKE?
JUST LIKE MR. DROSSELMEYER SAID,
I'M REALLY THINKING
THAT I DON'T WANT TO RETURN
MYTHO TO THE STORY.
-DUCK.
DUCK!
-FAKIR?
FAKIR!
-DUCK?
-FAKIR,
THE PENDANT WON'T COME OFF.
IT'S THE LAST
OF MYTHO'S HEART SHARDS.
AND MYTHO ASKED ME
TO GIVE IT BACK TO HIM, BUT...
MYTHO SAID HE WANTS TO MAKE RUE
HIS PRINCESS,
AND I KNOW HE WANTS TO SAVE HER
FROM THE RAVEN.
[ SOBS ]
[ Voice breaking ]
BUT IT JUST WON'T COME OFF.
ALL THIS IS MY FAULT.
BECAUSE I'M THINKING
THAT DEEP INSIDE MY HEART,
I DON'T WANT THE STORY
TO EVER END.
PIKE AND LILIE AND MR. CAT AND
THE OTHERS TURNED INTO CROWS,
BUT EVEN AFTER THAT...
[ CRYING ]
-IDIOT.
YOU'RE NOT THE ONLY ONE.
-WHAT?
-YOU'RE NOT THE ONLY ONE, DUCK.
I DON'T WANT TO --
NO, THE FACT OF THE MATTER
IS THAT NOBODY WANTS TO SEE
THE STORY COME TO AN END --
NOBODY, SAVE MYTHO HIMSELF.
I STILL CAN'T WRITE A STORY
ABOUT MYTHO, EITHER.
STOP BLAMING JUST YOURSELF.
EVERYONE IS SCARED OF BEING
RESTORED TO THEIR TRUE SELVES.
THEY'RE USED TO BEING GIVEN
ROLES IN STORIES
THAT SHELTER THEM
FROM THE BUSINESS OF LIVING.
THE REAL YOU...
IS A DUCK.
AND THE REAL ME...
IN THE END, THE REAL ME HAS BEEN
PROTECTED SINCE MY CHILDHOOD.
-HUH?
-I CAN'T PROTECT ANYONE.
BUT EVEN IF THAT
IS WHAT I AM TRULY LIKE,
I WANT TO END THE STORY
ONCE AND FOR ALL.
I WANT TO PROTECT MYTHO AND YOU
BECAUSE OF MY OWN FEELINGS,
NOT SOME ROLE GIVEN TO ME, EVEN
IF I USE UP ALL OF MY POWER.
-WHEN THAT HAPPENS, I'LL GO BACK
TO BEING JUST A BIRD.
AND I WON'T EVER STUDY BALLET
WITH EVERYBODY AGAIN.
-THAT'S FINE, ISN'T IT?
AFTER ALL,
THAT'S WHO YOU REALLY ARE.
-YEAH.
-AND EVEN AFTER THAT TIME COMES,
I WILL STAY BY YOUR SIDE
FOREVER.
-[ Voice breaking ] FAKIR.
[ Thinking ] IT'S STRANGE.
UNTIL A SHORT WHILE AGO,
I THOUGHT IT WAS OKAY FOR ME TO
SIMPLY VANISH, BUT NOW I'M WEAK.
BUT FOR SOME REASON, FAKIR
ALWAYS MAKES ME STRONGER...
SOMEHOW.
-LET'S GO BACK TO BEING
OUR TRUE SELVES NOW.
-YES.
-LET'S COMPOSE AN END
FOR THIS STORY,
NOT JUST FOR MYTHO'S SAKE,
BUT FOR OUR OWN SAKES, AS WELL.
-YES.
[ TING! ]
[ CLASP CLICKS ]
[ GASPS ]
IT CAME OFF.
HEY, THE PENDANT CAME OFF
JUST NOW, FAKIR.
-LET'S RETURN IT TO MYTHO.
[ RUMBLING ]
-AAH!
WHOA! AAAAAH!
-[ CHUCKLES EVILLY ]
THE SPELL
RUNS MUCH DEEPER THAN THAT.
-IT'S RUE.
RUE, I'M COMING TO GET YOU!
-HOLD ON.
-HUH?
LET'S GO BACK.
-WHAT ABOUT RUE?
-MYTHO WILL BE ABLE TO SAVE RUE.
OUR JOB IS TO SAVE MYTHO.
WE HAVE TO HURRY.
-RIGHT.
-THAT'S UZURA.
SHE'LL GUIDE US OUT OF HERE.
[ DISTANT DRUMMING ]
-HUH?
OH, ARE YOU OKAY, ZURA?
-THANK YOU SO MUCH, UZURA.
-YES, THANK YOU.
-YOU TOOK YOUR PENDANT OFF,
ZURA.
-UH-HUH. WE GOT TO GIVE IT BACK
TO MYTHO FAST.
-OH.
-FAKIR...
WILL YOU WRITE A STORY ABOUT ME
JUST ONE MORE TIME?
-HUH?
-THAT WAY,
WE'LL COMBINE OUR "WE
WANT TO PROTECT MYTHO" POWERS.
-COMBINE OUR POWERS, HUH?
-MM.
-IS IT REALLY OKAY FOR ME
TO WRITE A STORY ABOUT YOU?
-YEAH.
OKAY, THEN.
I'LL BE BACK.
-RIGHT.
-WELL, GOODBYE, UZURA.
ALL RIGHT.
OH.
HUH?
UZURA...
-PRINCESS TUTU, HUH?
[ DRUMMING ]
-HUH?
-HEY, DUCK!
DO YOUR BEST, ZURA!
-[ Thinking ] PRINCESS TUTU RAN,
DETERMINED TO RETURN THE LAST
HEART SHARD TO THE PRINCE.
SHE DIDN'T DO IT JUST FOR THE
PRINCE, BUT FOR ALL THE PEOPLE.
WHEN SHE THOUGHT OF IT THAT WAY,
THERE WAS NO MORE HESITATION.
[ TWINKLE! ]
THE MORNING BELL
HAD NOT YET RUNG.
THE PRINCE WAS QUIETLY WAITING
FOR TUTU TO COME.
-PRINCE, I'M SORRY
TO HAVE MADE YOU WAIT.
-I NEVER DOUBTED
YOU WOULD COME FOR ME.
-[ GASPS LIGHTLY ]
-THE FEELINGS
YOU RETURN TO ME --
THE FEELINGS OF LOVE,
AFFECTION, SORROW, LONELINESS --
ALL OF MY FEELINGS TOLD ME THAT
TUTU WAS SURE TO COME FOR ME.
[ TWINKLE! ]
-TUTU QUIETLY GAZED
INTO THE PRINCE'S EYES
THEN TOOK OFF THE PENDANT.
THE FINAL HEART SHARD
WAS SHAPED LIKE
A PAIR OF FLUTTERING WINGS --
WINGS FOR THE PEOPLE
WHO HAD SPENT A COMFORTABLE TIME
INSIDE THE STORY
TO LEAVE THE NEST WITH.
-WINGS FOR THE PRINCE
TO RETURN TO HIMSELF WITH.
[ TWINKLE! ]
-[ CHUCKLES ]
-GOODBYE NOW, MYTHO.
[ TWINKLE! ]
GOODBYE.
-TUTU...
-QUACK!
-YOU WERE...
-QUACK.
-SOMETHING SO SMALL AND FRAGILE
ACCOMPLISHED THIS.
THANK YOU, PRINCESS TUTU.
-QUACK?
-THIS IS THE TRUE PRINCE.
[ BELL TOLLING ]
-[ LAUGHS EVILLY ]
SO, YOU'VE FINALLY BEEN
RESTORED, PRINCE.
[ TWINKLE! ]
HMM?
[ LAUGHS EVILLY ]
-IT'S THE BEGINNING
OF A TRAGEDY.
THE PRINCE CAN'T FIGHT
FOR HIS PRINCESS' CAPTURE
INSIDE THE ENEMY.
TUTU HAS BECOME A MERE DUCK,
THE KNIGHT
HAS LONG BEEN USELESS,
AND THE PRINCESS WILL WASTE AWAY
IN THE DEPTHS OF DESPAIR.
WHAT WILL YOU DO NOW, PRINCE?
WILL YOU SHATTER YOUR HEART
A SECOND TIME?
[ CHUCKLES EVILLY ]
-[ SINGING IN JAPANESE ]
[ SINGING IN JAPANESE
CONTINUES ]
-THE REAL ME IS JUST A DUCK,
BUT I CAN STILL DANCE.
-NO ONE TO TRICK ME,
NO ONE FOR ME TO RESENT.
THERE'S NOTHING HERE,
NOT EVEN LOVING.
-EVERYTHING THAT HAPPENED
IN GOLD CROWN TOWN
THIS THING WAS RECORDING
AS A STORY.
-IN MY NAME AS PRINCE SIEGFRIED,
I CALL THE NAME OF THE PRINCESS!
-LET'S GIVE THIS STORY
A HAPPY ENDING.
-ALL YOU CHILDREN WHO LOVE
STORIES, COME, GATHER 'ROUND.
[ LAUGHS EVILLY ]