-ONCE UPON A TIME,
THERE WAS A MAIDEN
WITH WINGS OF FREEDOM.
A MAN IN LOVE WITH THIS MAIDEN
THOUGHT,
"IF I COULD JUST BIND
THOSE WINGS,
WE WOULD NEVER HAVE TO
BE APART, EVEN FOR A MOMENT."
BUT WHEN THE MAN WRAPPED
THE MAIDEN'S WINGS
IN A MAGICAL SHAWL,
THE WINGS IMMEDIATELY
FELL TO THE GROUND,
AND THE MAIDEN DIED.
THE MAN DID NOT KNOW
THAT THE MAIDEN'S WINGS
WERE THE SOURCE OF HER LIFE.
[ RITSUKO OKAZAKI'S
"MORNING GRACE" PLAYING ]
-♪ YONDE IRU KOE ♪
♪ SAA ME O SAMASHITE ♪
♪ NAKIGAO NUGUTTE ♪
♪ MABUSHII HIKARI ♪
♪ KIGI NO TSUYU ♪
♪ UMARERU ♪
♪ DARE MO SHIRANAI ♪
♪ HIMITSU NO MIZUBE DE ♪
♪ ODORE INOCHI NO PA DO DU ♪
♪ KYOU MO YUME MITERU ♪
♪ SORE WA YASASHIKU ♪
♪ HAGESHII NAGARE NE ♪
♪ DOKO MADE TSUZUKU RABIRINSU ♪
♪ WATASHI WA YUKOU ♪
♪ NIGIRISHIMERU YUME ♪
[ TCHAIKOVSKY'S
"WALTZ OF THE FLOWERS" PLAYING ]
-AT LAST, ALL THE CHARACTERS
NEEDED FOR THE STORY
HAVE BEEN ASSEMBLED.
A PRINCE WITHOUT THE HEART
TO LOVE,
A KNIGHT WHO FEARS DEATH,
A VILLAIN WITHOUT RESOLVE,
AND A PRINCESS WHO CANNOT
EXPRESS HER LOVE. [ LAUGHS ]
SOMETHING'S STILL MISSING,
THOUGH.
ALL RIGHT, YOU, GO ON,
AND THIS TIME,
DON'T YOU BECOME INTERESTED
IN PEOPLE'S EMOTIONS.
[ LAUGHS EVILLY ]
♪
[ MUSIC STOPS ]
-EXCUSE ME.
WON'T YOU PLEASE TAKE THIS?
-IT'S QUITE LOVELY.
-THE NAME OF THIS GEM
IS..."LOVE."
[ TINKLES ]
-LOVE?
I WOULD ADVISE YOU NOT
TO LET IT GO. IT SUITS YOU.
-NO, I HAD NO RIGHT TO BE
HOLDING ON TO SUCH A THING.
SOMEONE LIKE ME NEVER DID.
-I SEE.
THANK YOU.
[ BEETHOVEN'S
"CORIOLAN OVERTURE" PLAYING ]
♪
-[ Thinking ] PRINCESS TUTU...
IS HER?
-I DON'T HAVE ANY WISH
TO FIGHT YOU.
-[ Thinking ] IT DOESN'T MATTER
WHO PRINCESS TUTU IS.
I WILL PROTECT MYTHO
IN MY OWN WAY.
I'LL BE THE ONE GUARDING HIM
FROM THE CLUTCHES
OF THAT RAVEN....
WITHOUT FEAR.
-[ MOANS ]
I WONDER IF HE REALLY KNOWS NOW.
[ WHIMPERS ]
[ BIRDS CHIRPING ]
-[ SIGHS ]
-YOU'VE BEEN SIGHING
ALL MORNING.
-POOR THING. THE SCAR OF
REJECTION MUST TRULY RUN DEEP.
-YOU SEEM HAPPY.
-WHO, ME?
-THANKS FOR WORRYING ABOUT ME.
BUT IT'S NOT ABOUT BEING
REJECTED OR ANY --
-IT'S OKAY, DUCK.
YOU DON'T HAVE TO TELL US.
WE KNOW.
-ANYWAY, REVENGE! REVENGE!
COME ON, YOU'VE GOTTA DO IT.
-THAT'S RIGHT!
YOU'LL DO IT, WON'T YOU?
AT ANY RATE, YOU'LL HAVE TO
GET HIM TO NOTICE YOU.
-YEAH! AND THAT MEANS A PRESENT.
-OOH, THAT'S GOOD.
THEN YOU'LL SEE HOW
HE FEELS ABOUT YOU.
-REALLY?
-[ SCREAMS ]
-FAKIR, TOO.
-FAKIR?
-SO GIVING SOMEONE A PRESENT
WILL REVEAL THEIR FEELINGS
ABOUT YOU?
-OH, NO, YOU WERE LISTENING?
-HE HEARD US.
-GET A PRESENT NOW, AND HE'LL
SEE YOUR ULTERIOR MOTIVE.
-OH.
-WHEN YOU SAY "PRESENT,"
WHAT KIND OF THING DO YOU MEAN?
-[ GIGGLING ]
HE'S PROBING US.
-OH, WHAT DO WE DO?
-HOW DO YOU THINK
WE SHOULD ANSWER?
-[ GROANING ]
-SAY, DUCK, WHAT IF IT WERE YOU?
-[ SCREAMS ]
-DUCK WOULD TAKE ANYTHING
AROUND ME.
-THAT'S RIGHT.
SHE'D TAKE ANYTHING.
ANYTHING SHE COULD GET.
-AS LONG AS IT'S GIVEN
WITH LOVE.
-EVEN GEMS
OR BARS OF SOLID GOLD.
-LOVE? THERE NEEDS TO BE LOVE?
-MR. MYTHO,
I HELD A SPECIAL CLASS YESTERDAY
ON BEING IN LOVE.
PERHAPS, I NEED TO HOLD
A SPECIAL CLASS ON LOVE ITSELF.
-ARE YOU SAYING THAT
THERE'S A DIFFERENCE?
-OF COURSE THERE IS!
IF YOU DO NOT GRASP THAT,
YOU WILL NOT BE ABLE TO GET...
[ GROWLS ] MARRIED. [ MEOWS ]
[ GROANING ]
WOULD YOU CARE TO SIT IN
AS WELL, MR. FAKIR?
-NO, THANK YOU.
-THEN, MR. MYTHO, LET US GO.
GIFTS ARE PERFECTLY FINE
BUT SUCH THINGS AS ANTI-FLEA
COLLARS CAN BE RUDE,
SO DISCRETION IS NECESSARY.
-[ GASPING ]
-[ Thinking ]
DOES HE KNOW, AFTER ALL?
-[ GROANS ]
[ GASPS ] FAKIR!
-I WANNA ASK YOU SOMETHING.
FOLLOW ME.
-WHAT'D YOU WANNA ASK ME?
-PRINCESS TUTU.
-[ GULPS, MUFFLED SHOUT ]
-YOU ARE, AREN'T YOU?
-OH.
-HMM.
I'M SURPRISED, TO BE HONEST.
OF ALL THE PEOPLE,
I NEVER EXPECTED IT WAS YOU.
-I WANNA ASK YOU SOMETHING, TOO.
-HMM?
-JUST LIKE ME, YOU'RE FIGHTING
TO PROTECT MYTHO, AREN'T YOU?
THEN WHY DO YOU KEEP TRYING TO
SHATTER HIS HEART ALL THE TIME?
WHY?
-THAT IS SOMETHING
THAT HAS NO BEARING
ON THE PRESENT SITUATION,
UNDERSTAND?
THE TALE CAN NO LONGER
BE HALTED.
-THE TALE?
-IF YOU WISH TO RESTORE
HIS HEART, THEN GO AHEAD.
NO MATTER WHAT THE OUTCOME
OF YOUR LITTLE HEROICS,
I WILL PROTECT MYTHO.
-THEN WHY DON'T WE WORK
TOGETHER? AND THAT WAY --
-NO, THANK YOU.
-BUT, WHY NOT?
-TO PUT IT SIMPLY,
I DON'T TRUST YOU.
[ DOOR OPENS AND CLOSES ]
[ CAWING ]
[ INDISTINCT CONVERSATIONS ]
-[ Thinking ] MYTHO...
IF YOU REGAIN ANY MORE
OF YOUR HEART,
YOU'LL GROW DISTANT FROM ME.
I KNOW IT.
I AM A CROW, YOUR ENEMY,
EVEN THOUGH I LOVE YOU SO MUCH.
-I WISH I COULD'VE STAYED
RUE FOREVER,
FREE OF KRAEHE'S MEMORIES.
BUT NOW...
♪
-WOULD ANYONE LIKE SOME GEMS?
WOULD ANYONE LIKE A GEM TO GIVE
YOUR LOVED ONE AS A GIFT?
WELCOME.
-AREN'T YOU...
-IT'S BEEN A WHILE, RUE.
-AS A GIFT?
-HAS THIS ONE CAUGHT YOUR FANCY?
THE NAME OF THIS GEM
HERE IS "LOVE."
[ THUNDER CRASHES ]
-IT'S LOVE?
-I THINK IT'S BEAUTIFUL.
-SINCE YOU SEEM TO LIKE IT SO
MUCH, I SHALL GIVE IT TO YOU.
-ARE YOU SURE?
-I AM.
PLEASE TAKE THIS,
AS I HAVE NO USE FOR IT.
-WHY DON'T YOU ACCEPT IT, MYTHO?
-HMM.
-AND YET, THOUGH THIS GEM
IS STRONG, IT IS EASILY SCARRED.
THOUGH BEAUTIFUL,
IT IS EASILY TARNISHED.
IF FOUGHT OVER,
IT MAY PROVE DEADLY.
PLEASE USE CARE IN HANDLING IT.
-YOU REALLY LIKE IT THAT MUCH?
-HMM.
-SO...YOU'RE GOING TO GIVE IT
TO ME, AREN'T YOU?
-[ GASPS ]
-RUE...
SORRY, THIS IS...
[ RAVENS CAWING ]
-[ CHUCKLES ]
I WAS JUST KIDDING.
I SEE.
I WONDER WHO THE LUCKY GIRL IS.
-THAT'S NOT...
-COULD I SEE IT FOR A SECOND?
-SURE.
-IT'S BEAUTIFUL,
BUT IT SEEMS THERE'S
SOMETHING IMPORTANT MISSING.
I WONDER WHAT.
-WHAT? REALLY?
[ CLATTERS ]
-[ GASPS ]
-I'M SORRY.
I KNOW IT'S PRECIOUS TO YOU.
SAY, WOULD YOU LET ME
BORROW IT FOR TONIGHT?
I'LL FIX IT UP
AND MAKE IT EVEN PRETTIER,
SO THAT YOU CAN SECURE THE HEART
OF THE ONE YOU LOVE.
-OKAY.
-THE RESULTS OUGHT
TO PLEASE YOU.
[ CHUCKLES ]
[ CAWS, WINGS FLUTTER ]
-MYTHO, I WILL NOT
LET ANYONE ELSE HAVE YOU.
[ Thinking ]
I'LL NEVER HAND YOU OVER.
-VERY GOOD, VERY GOOD.
ANOTHER NECESSARY COMPONENT
OF THE TALE HAS BEEN ADDED.
LOVE FILLED WITH HATRED.
[ LAUGHS ]
OH, THIS IS AN INTERESTING
DEVICE, YES. [ LAUGHS ]
-[ Thinking ] FAKIR FOUND OUT.
BUT IT'S KIND OF STRANGE.
I ACTUALLY FEEL RELIEVED NOW.
-TO PUT IT SIMPLY,
I DON'T TRUST YOU.
-FAKIR'S ALWAYS
THINKING BY HIMSELF,
DECIDING BY HIMSELF,
FIGHTING BY HIMSELF,
EVEN...EVEN CRYING BY HIMSELF.
HE WON'T SHOW ME HIS TRUE FACE.
IT WAS WARM THERE
IN FAKIR'S ARMS.
I BET THAT'S THE REAL FAKIR.
-FAKIR?
-YES, WHAT?
-I'M THINKING OF GIVING
A GIFT TO TUTU.
-THAT SO?
-YOU'RE NOT ANGRY?
-DO AS YOU WISH.
-DON'T TURN YOUR SWORD
AGAINST TUTU AGAIN.
PLEASE, FAKIR.
I WANT YOU TO PROMISE ME.
-I CAN'T MAKE THAT PROMISE.
-[ SIGHS ]
[ BIRDS CHIRPING ]
-NOW, PLEASE DO NOT STOOP!
-YES, SIR!
-[ CHUCKLES ]
THANKS FOR WAITING.
WHAT DO YOU THINK?
-[ GASPS ]
IT'S WONDERFUL.
-ISN'T IT, THOUGH?
IF YOU GIVE THIS
TO THE ONE YOU LOVE,
YOU'LL BE ABLE TO SECURE
HER HEART NOW
AND FOR ALL TIME.
[ LAUGHS ]
-THANK YOU, RUE.
[ TCHAIKOVSKY'S "DANCE OF
THE SUGAR PLUM FAIRY" PLAYING ]
[ BELL CLANGING ]
-[ GROANS ]
I WISH I COULD GO HOME ONCE
WITHOUT HAVING TO STAY AFTER.
[ HORSE WHINNIES IN DISTANCE ]
-MYTHO!
WHOA!
[ HORSE WHINNIES ]
-WHOA!
[ THUDS ]
WHAT WAS THAT?
I DON'T KNOW WHAT HAPPENED,
BUT I BETTER GO AFTER HIM.
PROTECTING THE PRINCE IS ALSO
PRINCESS TUTU'S --
[ THUNDER CRASHES ]
-THUNDER?
-MYTHO DIDN'T HAVE AN UMBRELLA,
DID HE?
WHERE DID HE GO?
[ THUNDER CRASHES ]
-PRINCESS TUTU.
I WONDER WHERE SHE IS.
[ RAVENS CAWING IN DISTANCE ]
[ INDISTINCT CONVERSATIONS ]
[ WATER FLOWING ]
[ THUNDER CRASHES ]
[ WINGS FLUTTER ]
-I WONDER WHERE HE WENT.
♪
-WOULD ANYONE LIKE SOME GEMS?
-MISS EDEL!
HI, MISS EDEL!
-IT'S BEEN A WHILE, HASN'T IT?
-NOW THAT YOU MENTION IT,
IT HAS BEEN A WHILE.
-[ CHUCKLES ]
-ANYWAY, MISS EDEL,
HAVE YOU SEEN MYTHO AROUND?
-IF YOU WANT MYTHO,
HE'S SEARCHING FOR THE ONE
TO GIVE HIS GIFT TO.
-MYTHO'S GIFT?
-SO GIVING SOMEONE A PRESENT
WILL REVEAL THEIR FEELINGS
ABOUT YOU?
WHAT DO YOU THINK OF ME?
I WANT TO KNOW.
-I...UH, I...
THE ONE TO GIVE HIS GIFT TO?
OH, I KNOW! IT'S RUE, RIGHT?
WITH HIS FEELINGS COMING BACK,
HE PROBABLY WANTS TO KNOW
HOW RUE FEELS AND STUFF.
MM-HMM. THAT'S IT!
BUT IF THE GIFT WAS FOR TUTU...
WELL, EVEN IF THAT WERE TRUE,
IT'S NOT FOR ME AS DUCK
BUT FOR TUTU!
SO IT REALLY HAS NOTHING
TO DO WITH ME.
NOTHING TO DO WITH ME.
THANK YOU, MISS EDEL!
-[ SIGHS ]
-MAYBE HE'LL BE LOOKING
SOMEWHERE THAT HE MET TUTU.
[ WATER FLOWING ]
-[ PANTING ]
[ BIRDS CHIRPING ]
-MYTHO!
MYTHO, WHERE ARE YOU?
[ TINKLES ]
-[ Thinking ] TUTU.
CAN I NOT SEE YOU,
PRINCESS TUTU?
-TUTU.
-[ BREATHING HEAVILY ]
MYTHO!
-IS THAT DUCK?
-MYTHO.
-WHY HAVE YOU COME HERE?
-OH, IT SEEMED LIKE
IT MIGHT RAIN,
AND I THOUGHT YOU MIGHT NOT
HAVE AN UMBRELLA, SO I...
YOU WAITING FOR SOMEONE?
-YES, FOR PRINCESS TUTU.
-HUH?
-TELL ME, DUCK,
DO YOU KNOW ABOUT TUTU?
-WHAT? OH, NO. I DON'T. BUT...
-OH.
-UM...
-HMM?
-PLEASE USE THIS, OKAY?
-OH, THANK YOU.
-I HOPE YOU SEE HER.
-YES.
-BYE!
-[ BREATHING HEAVILY ] OH.
[ Thinking ] THE ONE MYTHO
WANTS TO SEE ISN'T ME.
IT'S PRINCESS TUTU, BUT...
-OH, MY, THAT'S DANGEROUS.
THAT THOUGHT IS TRULY DANGEROUS.
ARE YOU SURE ABOUT THIS,
PRINCESS TUTU?
[ CHIMES ]
[ BUBBLING ]
[ TINKLING ]
[ CHIMING ]
-MY PRINCE.
IS MY PRINCE SEARCHING
FOR SOMEBODY?
-TUTU.
-MY PRINCE.
-FINALLY, I GOT A CHANCE
TO SEE YOU.
-IT'S LOVELY.
-I'D LIKE FOR YOU
TO ACCEPT THIS.
-IF THAT IS WHAT
MY PRINCE WISHES.
-I'LL PUT IT ON YOU.
-ALL RIGHT.
[ CLASP LATCHES ]
-OH, THANK YOU.
-THAT'S STRANGE.
-WHAT IS?
-THEY SAID IF YOU GIVE SOMEONE
A GIFT,
YOU'LL KNOW HOW THEY FEEL.
BUT I STILL DON'T KNOW
HOW YOU FEEL.
I DON'T KNOW WHAT IT IS
YOU THINK OF ME.
-THAT...
-ALTHOUGH...
-HUH?
-IT MADE YOU HAPPY.
SO I THINK THAT'S OKAY, TOO.
-MY PRINCE.
[ CHIMES ]
-OH, WHAT?
THIS IS...
A HEART SHARD.
COME ON OUT.
WHAT FEELING ARE YOU
SUPPOSED TO BE?
-I AM THE FEELING OF LOVE.
-OH, THE FEELING OF LOVE.
-YOU ARE?
-YOU DON'T HAVE TO WANDER
ANY LONGER.
THE PLACE FOR YOU
TO RETURN TO IS HERE.
-I'M SO GLAD.
INSIDE THAT ORNAMENT, IT WAS
DARK AND THOSE TERRIFYING CROWS.
-[ GASPS ]
OH!
-[ SCREAMING ]
-[ GASPS ]
[ WIND BLOWING ]
-KRAEHE!
-THE FEELING OF LOVE, IS IT?
I WAS HOPING TO DISPATCH TUTU
WITH THE GEM
BUT LOOK WHAT TURNED UP.
AND NOW I KNOW YOUR IDENTITY.
[ RAVENS CAW ]
-[ GASPS ]
KRAEHE, WHAT ARE YOU DOING?
[ CAWING, WINGS FLUTTERING ]
-WHAT?
-FAKIR!
-BACK OFF, YOU RAVEN.
-OH, MY, THAT'S DANGEROUS.
THAT ACTION IS TRULY DANGEROUS.
YOU MAY BE THE KNIGHT REBORN,
BUT YOU'RE STILL JUST A HUMAN.
ARE YOU SURE OF THE COURSE
YOU'RE TAKING?
THEN AGAIN, THE PRINCESS IS ONLY
A MERE DUCK, ISN'T SHE?
AND THE PRINCE IS REALLY NOTHING
BUT A...STORY.
IT'S DANGEROUS NOT KNOWING
YOUR PLACE IN THE WORLD.
OH, YES, AND WHO MIGHT I ASK
ARE YOU, PRINCESS KRAEHE?
ARE YOU REALLY THE VILLAIN?
ARE YOU REALLY THE RAVEN?
HOW TRULY DANGEROUS.
DON'T YOU KNOW THE DANGER
YOU PUT YOURSELF IN NOT KNOWING
YOUR PLACE?
-STAY AWAY FROM MYTHO!
BE GONE, YOU UGLY CROW!
-[ GROANS ]
[ SWORD CLANGING ]
-AAH!
-KRAEHE!
[ SCREAMS ]
-[ GRUNTS ]
-[ SCREAMING ]
[ SWORD CLANGS ]
-FAKIR!
-[ LAUGHS ] YOU SEE?
WHAT DID I JUST SAY, HMM?
IF YOU'RE THE KNIGHT,
YOU HAVE TO CONQUER ANY FEARS
YOU HAVE AND DEFEAT THE VILLAIN.
IF YOU'RE THE VILLAIN,
YOU HAVE TO ELIMINATE
THE PRINCESS
WITHOUT ANY SHOW OF MERCY.
IF YOU'RE THE PRINCESS,
YOU HAVE TO SAVE THE PRINCE
BY THE POWER OF YOUR LOVE.
IF YOU'RE THE PRINCE,
YOU HAVE TO USE YOUR WISDOM
AND COURAGE.
OH! I KNEW SOMETHING
WAS MISSING.
-YES, I AM PRINCESS KRAEHE.
WHATEVER I WANT,
I WILL TAKE BY FORCE.
-WHAT ARE YOU INTENDING TO DO?
-[ GRUNTS ] KRAEHE!
[ GROANING ]
-HOW DO YOU LIKE IT,
PRINCESS TUTU,
BEING BOUND BY
THE PRINCE'S FEELINGS?
-WHAT?
-HURTS, YES?
WELL, THAT ONLY SHOWS HOW
STRONGLY HE FEELS FOR YOU.
HOW SHAMEFUL.
-[ GROANING ]
-NO, KRAEHE! STOP!
YOU LOVE THE PRINCE, RIGHT?
-[ EXHALES ]
-[ WHIMPERS ]
BUT WHY?
WHY WOULD YOU DO SOMETHING
SO HORRIBLE?
[ WIND BLOWS ]
-OH, DEAR. THE ENEMY NOW KNOWS
YOUR IDENTITY,
AND YOU'VE LOST THE PRINCE.
HOW DELIGHTFUL, HOW TERRIBLE.
[ LAUGHS ]
[ RITSUKO OKAZAKI'S "ALTHOUGH
MY LOVE IS SMALL" PLAYING ]
-♪ YUME MIRU ♪
♪ YOU NI ♪
♪ KOI O SHITA NO ♪
♪ FUKURAMU ♪
♪ KOKORO GA FUKURAMU NO YO ♪
♪ IKITERUTTE SUTEKI
NA KOTO TO OMOTTA ♪
♪ ASU GA MACHI DOOSHII ♪
♪ MM ♪
♪ ANATA NO CHIKARA NI NARITAI
NO DONNA TOKI NI MO WATASHI ♪
♪ MATTE MATTE
KURENAI HASHITTE ♪
♪ HASHITTE IKU NO YO ♪
♪ KAZE MO AMAGUMO
MO OIKOSHITE ♪
♪ WATASHI DAKE
NO TSUBASA HABATAITE ♪
-ONE TIME,
WHEN I'D LOST THIS NECKLACE,
YOU HELD ON TO IT FOR ME.
REMEMBER, FAKIR?
WOULD YOU HOLD ON TO IT AGAIN?
-IT CAN'T BE. THAT DUCK?
-QUACK!
-HAVE YOU REGRESSED TO THE DOLL
YOU USED TO BE?
BECAUSE I WITHDREW THAT
PIECE OF YOUR HEART.
-BUT THIS SAME KNIGHT
WAS TORN IN TWO
BY THE CLAWS OF THE RAVEN,
WITHOUT THE KNIGHT EVEN LANDING
A SINGLE BLOW WITH HIS SWORD.
A USELESS WRETCH WHO COULD
ONLY TALK OF PROTECTION.
-PLEASE,
STOP THIS MALEVOLENCE NOW!
-ALL YOU CHILDREN WHO LOVE
STORIES, COME GATHER 'ROUND.
[ LAUGHS EVILLY ]