-ONCE UPON A TIME,
A WITCH LAID A CURSE,
WHICH CAST A PRINCESS
INTO AN ETERNAL SLUMBER.
ONE DAY, A YOUNG MAN APPEARED,
INTENDING TO AWAKE HER.
BUT THEN A VOICE WHISPERS,
"AWAKEN THE PRINCESS
FROM HER SLEEP?
"WHAT A CRUEL THING TO DO...
"FOR WHAT IF THE PRINCESS WISHES
"NOT TO RECEIVE THE KISS
OF AWAKENING,
BUT RATHER TO CONTINUE
TO SLEEP FOREVER?"
[ RITSUKO OKAZAKI'S
"MORNING GRACE" PLAYS ]
-[ SINGING IN JAPANESE ]
[ SINGING CONTINUES ]
[ TCHAIKOVSKY'S "FINAL
WALTZ AND APOTHEOSIS" FROM
"THE NUTCRACKER" PLAYS ]
[ BIRDS CHIRPING ]
[ TCHAIKOVSKY'S "DANCE OF
THE SUGAR PLUM FAIRY" PLAYS ]
-SO, YOU'RE AWAKE.
-FAKIR.
-WHAT IS IT?
-I WONDER WHAT IT IS
I THINK OF YOU, FAKIR.
WHEN I THINK OF RUE,
WHEN I THINK OF YOU, FAKIR,
AND WHEN I'M THINKING
ABOUT PRINCESS TUTU,
EACH ONE MAKES ME FEEL
DIFFERENT.
BUT I DON'T KNOW WHAT NAMES
I SHOULD GIVE THESE FEELINGS.
TELL ME, FAKIR.
DON'T I NEED TO KNOW
WHAT THEY ARE?
-STOP BROODING ON NONSENSE.
-BUT --
-YOU LISTEN TO ME,
YOU USELESS, GOOD-FOR-NOTH--
WHAT'S THIS?
YOU'RE TREMBLING.
-[ SIGHS ]
I JUST COULDN'T SLEEP SOMEHOW.
I SAW MYTHO SMILE.
I GUESS FOR RUE, AT LEAST,
HE'LL SMILE LIKE THAT.
THERE'S NO WAY THAT MYTHO
DOESN'T NEED A HEART.
HMM?
MYTHO?
[ WINDOW CREAKS ]
I'LL GET YOUR HEART BACK
FOR YOU.
[ GASPS ] FAKIR!
JUST WHAT IS HE PLOTTING?
TRICKING MYTHO INTO OBEYING HIM.
OR IS IT SOMETHING ELSE
COMPLETELY?
[ WINDOW CREAKS ]
WHATEVER YOU'RE PLOTTING,
IT'S NO USE.
PRINCESS TUTU WILL GET
ALL OF MYTHO'S HEART AND --
[ GASPS ] AAH!
[ SPARKLE! ]
[ WHIMPERING ]
AAH!
[ SPARKLE! ]
[ SWIRL! SWIRL! SWIRL! ]
-DUCK! DUCK! LET'S GO!
MAYBE SHE'S MISTOOK THE TIME
AND LEFT EARLY AGAIN.
[ SWIRL! SWIRL! ]
[ BELL TOLLING ]
[ INDISTINCT CONVERSATIONS ]
-A THEATER TROUPE?
-SAY, IT'S THE ELEKI TROUPE.
-NEVER HEARD OF THEM.
-"SLEEPING BEAUTY," HUH?
[ SPARKLE! ]
-WE ARE A TOURING BALLET
COMPANY.
STARTING THE DAY AFTER TOMORROW,
WE WILL BE PERFORMING "SLEEPING
BEAUTY" AT THIS THEATER.
PLEASE COME AND SEE US.
[ CROWD MURMURING ]
TILL THEN, ADIEU!
[ INDISTINCT SHOUTING ]
-ALL RIGHT!
-DID YOU SEE THE FLYERS
FOR THE ELEKI TROUPE?
-SHE LOOKED SO PRETTY!
-THEY'RE PERFORMING IN TOWN!
I SO WANT TO SEE THIS!
-[ CLEARS THROAT ]
TODAY WE'VE RECEIVED
SPECIAL PERMISSION
FOR BOTH THE BOYS AND GIRLS
TO COME
TO THE ELEKI TROUPE'S REHEARSAL
FOR OBSERVATION PURPOSES.
I HOPE YOU TAKE THIS CHANCE
TO GET A TASTE OF FOREIGN BALLET
AND USE THAT TO HELP
GET YOU OFF THE GROUND.
DON'T YOU THINK SO, MISS DUCK?
-UH, WELL, YOU SEE --
-DON'T YOU THINK?
-OH, YES. YOU'RE RIGHT.
I DON'T THINK SO, EITHER.
-YOU DON'T THINK SO?
-YES, YOU ARE ABSOLUTELY RIGHT.
I DON'T THINK SO AT ALL.
-ABOUT WHAT DO YOU NOT THINK SO?
-YES. WELL, UH,
ABOUT WANTING TO MARRY YOU.
WAS THAT WRONG?
-MYTHO, YOU GO BACK
TO YOUR ROOM.
-MM.
[ INDISTINCT CONVERSATIONS ]
-MR. CAT'S ALL DEPRESSED NOW.
-HE MAY NOT BOUNCE BACK.
-HMM.
YOU SAD 'CAUSE MYTHO'S NOT HERE?
-MM-HMM.
-OH!
-FAKIR CAME ALONE.
-DO FAKIR'S ACTIONS BOTHER YOU?
-MM.
-[ GASPS ]
-HUH?
-YOU SAID YOU WEREN'T INTERESTED
IN FAKIR.
-SHE'S AT THAT AGE.
WHAT'S WRONG WITH THAT?
-IT'S JUST WRONG.
YOU'RE ALL LOVEY-DOVEY FOR
MYTHO, AREN'T YOU? AREN'T YOU?
-YOU DON'T EVEN KNOW
YOUR OWN PLACE. HOW CUTE.
-SO, WHICH ONE DO YOU
REALLY LOVE, HUH?
-SHE LOVES THEM BOTH.
SHE'S TWO-TIMING.
-[ Thinking ] LOVE?!
IT'S REALLY N-NOT
ANYTHING LIKE THAT!
AAH!
[ WOBBLE! ]
UGH!
HUH?
[ SPARKLE ]
-THAT'S QUITE SOME ENERGY.
-UH...SO...
[ GIRLS MURMURING ]
-MAN, SHE'S ONE LUCKY DUCK!
-THREE-TIMING!
-I'M PAULAMONI,
THE LEADING LADY.
NICE TO MEET YOU.
-PLEASE ACCEPT
OUR DEEPEST THANKS
FOR SHARING YOUR TIME WITH US
TODAY, MISS --
-LET'S DISPENSE WITH FORMALITY.
-I AGREE.
-MAKE YOURSELVES AT HOME.
-[ GASPS ] IT'S COME.
IT'S FINALLY COME,
THE PREMONITION OF LOVE!
REJOICE...
-I'D LIKE YOU TO MEET
MY HUSBAND -- PAULO.
-NICE TO MEET YOU.
-AAAAAAAH!
-NOW, COME RIGHT ON IN.
[ INDISTINCT CONVERSATIONS ]
-LOOK AT THIS PLACE.
-...PRETTY DRESS.
-OH, SO PRETTY!
-YOU'RE SO LUCKY.
YOU GOT TO BE HELD
LIKE A PRINCESS.
-I CAN'T BREATHE!
-OH, DUCK, IF ALL YOU WANTED
WAS TO BE HELD,
YOU KNOW I WOULD HAVE HELD YOU!
-HUH?!
-I'M AFRAID OF THE DARK!
-HOLD ON ONE SECOND.
-AAH!
[ THUDDING ]
[ GIRLS GASP ]
[ ELECTRICITY ZAPPING ]
-ELECTRIC EEL?
-SAY HELLO TO OUR TROUPE LEADER
AND ELECTRICAL GUY.
-TROUPE LEADER?
[ ZAPPING STOPS ]
-HUH?
[ ELECTRICITY ZAPPING ]
-[ GASPS ]
-STEADY SUPPLY.
[ THUDDING ]
I HAVE TO HIT IT
AT JUST THE RIGHT ANGLE.
-SAY, WAS OUR TROUPE LEADER
REALLY AN EEL?
-WHAT?
COME TO THINK OF IT,
BEFORE WE CAME HERE...
NO, THAT CAN'T BE RIGHT.
-WELL, IT'LL SAVE
ON THE POWER BILL.
[ LAUGHS ]
-THAT'S TRUE.
[ BALLET MUSIC PLAYING ]
[ SPARKLE! ]
-AHH.
-[ Thinking ]
IS RUE PRINCESS TUTU?
[ MUSIC CONTINUES ]
-WHAT?
[ GASPS ]
-WHAT'S WRONG?
-OH!
-IS SHE OKAY?
-IT'S NOTHING.
I'M SORRY.
[ GIRLS MURMURING ]
-REALLY?
THEN LET'S CONTINUE.
[ CLAPPING ]
-SAY, JUST WATCHING IS BORING,
ISN'T IT?
LET'S SEE SOMEONE ELSE.
-HUH?
-OH, MY GOD.
-IS SHE SERIOUS?
[ GIRLS MURMURING ]
-PAULAMONI, THIS IS TOO SUDDEN.
-WHAT DOES IT MATTER?
I WANT TO SEE.
-BUT --
-CERTAINLY.
I SHALL SHOW YOU THE RESULTS
OF MY LESSONS.
NOW, ARE THERE ANY VOLUNTEERS?
-YOUR CHANCE TO EARN
BROWNIE POINTS!
-HUH?
-LOSING WON'T HURT YOU!
-NO, NO, NO.
I CAN'T! I CAN'T! I CAN'T!
-IT CANNOT BE HELPED, THEN.
I WILL SELECT SOMEONE.
MISS R--
-YOU.
-[ SQUEALS ]
-UH, UH, UH...
-WHAT?!
-WHAT DO YOU SAY?
-AAH! I CAN'T DO IT!
NO WAY! NO WAY!
[ PLONK! PLONK! PLONK! ]
NO WAY!
-THERE YOU HAVE IT!
EVEN SHE HERSELF SAYS SHE CAN'T,
SO LET'S NOT FORCE HER.
PLEASE ENJOY
ANOTHER STUDENT'S DANCE!
IF YOU LIKE,
I'LL PERFORM MYSELF!
-AH. I GUESS IT WAS TOO SUDDEN.
I'M SO SORRY!
-NO! WE'LL DANCE!
-[ GROANING ]
-WE WERE WANTING TO DANCE!
WE WERE.
-[ GASPS ]
-REALLY, IT'S ALL RIGHT.
-THAT SURE SCARED ME.
-[ GRUNTING ]
-IT'S A HEART SHARD.
OR...WAS IT?
-WE'LL HAVE A RUN-THROUGH
TOMORROW, SO PLEASE COME WATCH.
-WE WILL, GLADLY!
-[ Thinking ] I'M ALWAYS NERVOUS
WHEN I GET UP ONSTAGE.
BUT I'VE NEVER FELT LIKE THIS.
[ CHEERS AND APPLAUSE ]
-SHE'S BEAUTIFUL.
-WHEN I WAS A CHILD,
I SAW PRINCESS AURORA
AND INSTANTLY FELL IN LOVE.
EVEN AFTER WAKING, SHE STILL
SEEMED TO BE IN A DREAM.
I WANTED TO BECOME LIKE THAT
SOMEDAY,
SO I'VE DANCED THE PART
OF AURORA ALL THIS TIME,
BUT...I'VE BEGUN TO SEE
THAT IT WAS NO USE,
NO MATTER HOW I POLISHED
MY TECHNIQUE.
I SIMPLY WASN'T BORN WITH
THE SAME TALENT.
I KNEW MY DREAM
WOULD NEVER COME TRUE,
BUT NO MATTER HOW DEPRESSED
I'D BEEN,
IT HAD NEVER TAKEN ME LIKE THIS.
WHAT'S THE MATTER WITH ME?
AM I AFRAID OF PERFORMING?
[ KNOCK ON DOOR ]
-[ Muffled ] HEY, PAULAMONI!
-YES?
-WE'RE MAKING DINNER.
WILL YOU HELP ME?
-SURE.
-MWAH!
[ FOOTSTEPS DEPARTING ]
[ BIRDS CHIRPING ]
-MMM.
[ CHUCKLES ]
-MMM, THAT SMELLS GREAT...
THOUGH IF WE DON'T FEED
OUR TROUPE LEADER SOON,
WE'LL HAVE AN OUTAGE.
-[ CHUCKLES ]
-THE PREMIER --
SHOULD WE POSTPONE?
THERE'S SOMETHING ON YOUR MIND,
RIGHT?
-THANKS FOR WORRYING ABOUT ME,
BUT I DON'T WANT TO TROUBLE
EVERYONE ELSE.
DON'T WORRY.
I CAN STILL DO IT.
-HMM.
[ BIRD SQUAWKING ]
-WOULD ANYONE LIKE SOME GEMS?
BEAUTIFUL, PRECIOUS GEMS.
-I DIDN'T KNOW YOU SOLD GEMS,
MISS EDEL.
-[ GIGGLES ]
-WELL, FAKIR SAID MYTHO
DOESN'T NEED A HEART,
BUT THAT CAN'T BE RIGHT.
HE'S WEIRD, REAL WEIRD!
I MEAN, REALLY.
MYTHO DOESN'T KNOW HOW IT FEELS
TO BE IN LOVE,
EVEN THOUGH RUE TRULY LOVES HIM.
ISN'T IT SAD?
-IS IT SAD?
-YOU THINK SO, DON'T YOU?
-IS IT SAD FOR MYTHO, RUE,
OR FOR YOU, DUCK?
-WHAT?
I'M NOT REALLY...
ANYWAY, NO MATTER WHAT
FAKIR DOES TO GET IN MY WAY,
I WILL GET ALL OF MYTHO'S HEART
BACK TO HIM.
I MAY NOT BE ABLE TO MAKE
MYTHO HAPPY LIKE RUE CAN
SINCE I'M JUST A BIRD,
BUT AT LEAST I CAN DO THIS.
HUH?
PRETTY!
-THE NAME OF THIS GEM
IS "DREAM."
YET WHO IS HAPPIER -- A DREAMER
WHO LINGERS OR ONE WHO IS WOKEN?
-HUH?
WHO WOULD BE?
ANYWAY, WHAT'S THIS GEM CALLED?
-HOPE.
-THIS ONE?
-ADVENTURE.
-AND THIS ONE?
-MYSTERY.
-OKAY. WHAT ABOUT THIS?
-AUTHOR'S BYPASS.
-HUH. STRANGE NAME.
OKAY!
IN ANY CASE, MY WISH IS
TO GET MYTHO TO SMILE AGAIN,
AND THAT'S ALL!
BYE!
[ Thinking ] THAT'S RIGHT.
I'M GOING TO WORK HARDER
AND GET ALL THE SHARDS
OF MYTHO'S HEART BACK FOR HIM!
ALL RIGHT, GO FOR IT, DUCK!
OW!
YES, I'LL DO MY BEST!
[ WIGGLE! ]
[ TCHAIKOVSKY'S
"NUTCRACKER SUITE" PLAYS ]
[ CURTAINS RUSTLE ]
-MYTHO.
-YES?
-GO ON TOMORROW'S FIELD TRIP.
-I CAN?
-AND MAKE SURE THAT YOU IGNORE
WHAT RUE SAYS.
-YES.
-I'LL BE THERE, TOO.
NOW GO TO SLEEP.
-YES, FAKIR.
THANK YOU.
-UH...IDIOT.
[ FOOTSTEPS APPROACHING ]
-[ GASPS ]
-YOU KNOW THE GIRL YOU CALLED ON
TODAY?
I HONESTLY WANTED TO SEE
HER DANCE, TOO.
SHE HAD THIS GLOW,
SORT OF A MYSTERIOUS,
INNATE CHARM, YOU KNOW?
-AND INNATE CHARM.
YES.
I'M SURE SHE'S PURSUING
A WONDERFUL DREAM.
AND CHANCES ARE
THAT SHE'S ALSO IN LOVE.
I CAN TELL.
-YOU SURE CAN TELL A LOT.
-YEAH.
BECAUSE YOU WERE THE SAME
WHEN YOU WERE YOUNGER.
-UH...
[ CHUCKLES ]
YOU'LL ALWAYS WAKE FROM A DREAM.
NO. YOU MUST WAKE UP.
-IN THAT CASE,
YOU SHOULDN'T PLAY AURORA.
-THAT WAS RATHER BLUNT.
-WELL, THE AURORA
YOU'VE BEEN ASPIRING TO
IS THE KIND OF GIRL
WHO CONTINUES TO DREAM
EVEN AFTER SHE'S WOKEN UP
FROM HER DREAM, CORRECT?
-[ GASPS ]
-BUT YOU'RE AFRAID
TO EVEN DREAM.
-BECAUSE I CAN'T BECOME
THAT PRINCESS AURORA.
-SURE, THERE ARE SOME DREAMS
THAT WON'T COME TRUE.
BUT THERE'S NO RULE THAT SAYS
YOU CAN ONLY HAVE ONE DREAM.
-WHAT?
-MY DREAM IS THIS --
TO ENTHRALL PEOPLE ALL OVER
THE WORLD WITH YOUR DANCING.
-[ EXHALES SHARPLY ]
-AND DO THAT, I'VE EVEN THOUGHT
UP THE PERFECT PROGRAM FOR YOU.
-PERFECT FOR ME?
-SO, PAULAMONI,
WHAT DO YOU SAY TO SHARING
A DREAM BETWEEN THE TWO OF US?
-I'D NO IDEA.
YOU REALLY WANT TO DO ALL THIS?
-I HAVEN'T WOKEN YET
FROM MY DREAM OR MY LOVE.
-PAULO.
THANK YOU, PAULO!
I'LL DANCE MY FINAL TURN
AS AURORA IN THIS TOWN.
-YES. AND IT WILL BE YOUR BEST.
[ DRAMATIC MUSIC PLAYING ]
-PLEASE DO NOT WORRY.
NO MATTER HOW THE WICKED WITCH
MAY CURSE ME,
I WILL SURELY NEVER PRICK
MY FINGER ON A SPINDLE...
FOR, THOUGH I MAY DREAM
AND DANCE ALL MY DAYS,
I WILL NEVER LAY MY HAND
ON A SPINNING WHEEL.
-[ Thinking ] THAT SMILE.
WAS THAT BECAUSE HE WAS DANCING
WITH ME OR...?
-HMM? OUR LEADER'S HOPELESS.
ALL RIGHT!
EVERYONE, LET'S TAKE A BREAK!
[ WATER BUBBLING ]
-MR. CAT.
-YEAH?
[ GASPS ] CAN I HELP YOU?
-I'D LIKE TO SPEAK WITH YOU.
-WHAT?!
YOU'D LIKE TO SPEAK WITH ME?!
-YES.
-NO! YOU MUSTN'T!
U-UNLESS, OF COURSE, YOU INSIST!
THAT IS, IN WHICH CASE --
[ STAMMERING ]
-THAT GIRL FROM YESTERDAY --
I WAS HOPING YOU MIGHT ALLOW ME
TO WATCH HER DANCE.
-OH.
-I WANT TO SEE IF I CAN FIND OUT
WHAT IT IS THAT MY PERFORMANCE
IS LACKING.
[ WOBBLE! ]
-ARE YOU SURE?!
[ TING! ]
SO, WHY'D SHE PICK ME?
-YES, I AGREE.
-BUT SOMEONE ELSE WOULD BE --
-BUT I'M REALLY BAD AT THIS,
SO --
-YES, I KNOW.
THIS IS AN EARNEST REQUEST
FROM MISS PAULAMONI.
DON'T WORRY, PLEASE.
DANCE TO YOUR HEART'S CONTENT.
EVEN IF MY DREAMS OF LOVE
WERE TO END BECAUSE OF IT,
I WILL NEVER...HOLD THAT MOST
PAINFUL FACT AGAINST YOU.
[ ZIP! ]
-BEEN AWHILE SINCE
HER LAST PINCH!
-I'VE WAITED FOR THIS!
-SAY, MYTHO,
WHY DON'T YOU PARTNER WITH HER
FOR THE PAS DE DEUX?
-WHAT? WITH MYTHO?
-NO. MYTHO WILL STAY.
I'LL GO.
-[ SIGHS ]
-WHY? WHY DID HE HAVE TO BUTT IN
LIKE THAT?
[ DRAMATIC BALLET MUSIC
PLAYING ]
[ WHIMPERS ]
[ ELECTRICITY ZAPPING ]
-OOH. OUR LEADER'S
APPROVAL GAUGE IS MAXED OUT.
-[ Thinking ]
RUE, WHAT ARE YOU THINKING?
-[ GASPING ]
[ GASPS ]
[ MUSIC CONTINUES ]
-[ Thinking ]
[ SCOFFS ] PATHETIC.
-[ EXHALES SHARPLY ]
-LET ME TAKE THIS CHANCE
TO MAKE THINGS CLEAR.
-WHAT?
-STAY AWAY FROM MYTHO.
-[ GASPS ]
YOU STAY AWAY FROM HIM.
[ GASPING ]
[ SQUEALS ]
AAH!
-YOU'RE AN EYESORE.
[ FLAP! FLAP! FLAP! ]
-THAT'S IT.
THIS GIRL'S DANCING IS
HARDLY ELEGANT,
BUT IT'S OVERFLOWING
WITH HER OWN INDIVIDUALITY.
[ SOFT BALLET MUSIC PLAYS ]
-MM.
-[ GASPS ]
MYTHO'S HEART!
AAH! AAH!
[ THUDS ]
OW.
[ GASPS ]
-ARE YOU ALL RIGHT?
-WHAT? OH, YES!
-I'M SORRY FOR FORCING YOU.
YOU DID GREAT.
ARE YOU HURT?
-UH, NO. I FEEL FINE.
UM, UH, WHERE'S THE BATHROOM?
-JUST GO OUT THOSE DOORS,
TURN LEFT,
AND THERE AT THE END OF THE HALL
YOU'LL SEE --
-THANK YOU!
[ SPECTATORS MURMURING ]
-HUH.
-[ GASPING ]
[ WHIMPERS ]
-UH-OH.
IS THE PRINCE'S HEART
RUNNING AWAY NOW?
I WONDER WHAT IT COULD BE
SO AFRAID OF.
PRINCESS TUTU?
[ SPARKLE! ]
[ WATER BUBBLING ]
[ SPARKLE! SPARKLE! SPARKLE! ]
[ SPARKLE! SPARKLE! ]
[ SOFT BALLET MUSIC CONTINUES ]
-PLEASE WAIT!
[ SPARKLE! ]
WHY DO YOU RUN AWAY?
[ FLUTTER! ]
[ SPARKLE! ]
[ DOOR OPENS ]
NOW LET ME BRING YOU BACK
TO WHERE YOU BELONG.
-I WON'T. I'M SCARED.
-NO. YOU HAVE TO.
-B-BUT WHY?
-YOU JUST DO.
-WHAT FOR?
-SO MYTHO CAN SMILE.
I CAN TAKE YOU BACK.
NOW COME HERE.
COME HERE!
[ WHIRL! ]
[ GASPS ]
-NO!
-[ BREATHING HEAVILY ]
[ SPARKLE! ]
NOW GO BACK.
RETURN TO MYTHO.
[ SPARKLE! SPARKLE! SPARKLE! ]
-[ GASPING ]
AAH!
-MYTHO!
-A SHARD'S BEEN RETURNED.
-WHAT?
-EVERYONE, PLEASE STAY CALM.
-AAH!
-WHAT?
-[ WHIMPERS ]
-HUH?
-HANG ON, MYTHO.
DAMN IT, PRINCESS TUTU.
-[ WHIMPERS ]
QUACK!
-[ GASPING, CRYING ]
I'M SCARED. I'M SCARED.
-CALM DOWN.
-WHAT'S HAPPENED TO MYTHO?
-IT'S ALL RIGHT.
I'M THE ONLY ONE HERE.
WHAT'S WRONG? WHAT SCARES YOU?
TELL ME.
-TUTU.
-[ GASPS ]
-I'M AFRAID...OF PRINCESS TUTU.
I'M AFRAID OF PRINCESS TUTU.
-WHAT? [ GASPS ]
THAT CAN'T BE.
-FEAR.
UNCERTAINTY.
YET ANOTHER SHARD
HAS BEEN RETURNED.
BUT THE PRINCE SEEMS RATHER SAD.
[ CHUCKLES ]
I WONDER WHAT'S GOING TO COME
OF THIS LITTLE INCIDENT.
[ LAUGHS EVILLY ]
[ SPARKLE! ]
-WHY THIS?
I JUST RETURNED A SHARD
OF HIS HEART.
WHY WAS MYTHO CRYING?
WHY WAS HE SUFFERING
IN SUCH PAIN?
WHAT'S GOING TO HAPPEN TO HIM?
[ Voice breaking ] I DIDN'T --
I JUST WANTED MYTHO TO SMILE.
THAT'S ALL I WANTED.
[ GASPS ]
WAS IT BAD?
WAS IT WRONG TO WANT THAT?
HAVE I JUST DONE
SOMETHING TERRIBLE TO MYTHO?
[ CRYING ]
-THAT'S RIGHT.
THIS IS HOW THE STORY
MOVES ALONG,
IN A DIRECTION MOST UNDESIRABLE
FOR ALL CONCERNED PARTIES.
[ LAUGHS EVILLY ]
[ SLOW MUSIC PLAYS ]
-[ SINGING IN JAPANESE ]
-BEING PRINCESS TUTU
IS MEANINGLESS!
-THE ONLY ONE I'VE EVER
HAD EYES FOR IS MYTHO.
I'M STILL FAR
FROM HAVING LOVED HIM ENOUGH.
- I PROMISE TO NEVER
APPEAR BEFORE YOU AGAIN,
SO DON'T WORRY.
-THESE ARE THE FEELINGS
OF LONELINESS AND OF SORROW.
-WHO ARE YOU?
-PRINCESS KRAEHE.
-I SEE. SO, YOU'VE FINALLY MADE
AN APPEARANCE.
-I WILL GIVE YOU NOTHING.
I WILL LET YOU DO NOTHING.
-ALL WHO LOVE STORIES,
GATHER 'ROUND.
[ LAUGHS EVILLY ]