-ONCE UPON A TIME,
THERE WAS A HANDSOME SLAVE.
WHAT BOUND HIM WERE NOT
HEAVY CHAINS,
BUT THE LOVE OF A PRINCESS.
EVERY DAY, EVERY NIGHT,
THE PRINCESS WHISPERED HER LOVE
TO THE SLAVE.
AND THE SLAVE RESPONDED
IN KIND.
BOUND BODY, BOUND EMOTIONS.
THE SLAVE OR THE PRINCESS --
WHICH OF THEM IS REALLY THE ONE
WHO IS UNABLE TO MOVE?
[ RITSUKO OKAZAKI'S
"MORNING GRACE" PLAYING ]
-♪ YONDE IRU KOE ♪
♪ SAA ME O SAMASHITE ♪
♪ NAKIGAO NUGUTTE ♪
♪ MABUSHII HIKARI ♪
♪ KIGI NO TSUYU ♪
♪ UMARERU ♪
♪ DARE MO SHIRANAI ♪
♪ HIMITSU NO MIZUBE DE ♪
♪ ODORE INOCHI NO PA DO DU ♪
♪ KYOU MO YUME MITERU ♪
♪ SORE WA YASASHIKU ♪
♪ HAGESHII NAGARE NE ♪
♪ DOKO MADE TSUZUKU RABIRINSU ♪
♪ WATASHI WA YUKOU ♪
♪ NIGIRISHIMERU YUME ♪
[ TCHAIKOVSKY'S
"WALTZ OF THE FLOWERS" PLAYING ]
[ THUNDER RUMBLING ]
-[ INHALES SHARPLY ]
[ GRUNTS ] HOW DID I...
[ BIRDS SQUAWKING ]
-[ GRUNTS ] LET GO OF ME.
I CAN WALK BY MYSELF.
-NO.
-THAT'S RIGHT.
PRINCESS TUTU HELPED ME,
AND THEN...
HUH?
BINDING MY WOUNDS.
WHAT KIND OF A USELESS CH-
HEY.
-MM.
OH. FAKIR. HOW ARE YOU?
-DON'T GIVE ME THAT.
WHY ARE YOU STILL TUTU?
-WHAT? OH.
I THOUGHT IT MIGHT BE BAD
IF I WENT IN THE BOYS' DORM ROOM
LOOKING LIKE NORMAL.
UH, W-WAS THAT WEIRD?
-[ SIGHS ] NO.
SORRY FOR HAVING TROUBLED YOU
WITH THIS.
-IT WAS NO TROUBLE.
OH! YOU'RE ABLE TO GET UP THEN.
-[ SCOFFS ] HEY, LISTEN.
THIS DOESN'T MEAN I PLAN ON
COOPERATING WITH YOU.
-BUT YOU'RE GOING OUT
TO LOOK FOR MYTHO, AREN'T YOU?
-UM...
-WE COULD AT LEAST COOPERATE
ON THAT, RIGHT?
LET'S LOOK FOR MYTHO TOGETHER.
-YOU CAN FORGET ABOUT
EVERYTHING.
ALL YOU NEED TO FILL THAT VOID
IS HERE IN MY ARMS.
NO ONE SHALL ENTER HERE.
IT SHALL JUST BE YOU AND ME.
SO I AM THE ONLY ONE THAT
YOU HAVE TO GIVE YOUR LOVE TO.
NOW TELL ME THAT YOU LOVE
ONLY ME.
-I LOVE ONLY YOU, KRAEHE.
NOBODY ELSE.
-HONESTLY?
-HONESTLY.
-BUT THAT...HOW MUCH?
IF YOU LOVE ME,
THEN SMILE FOR ME.
DON'T YOU REMEMBER THE FESTIVAL?
-HOW?
-HAVE YOU REGRESSED TO THE DOLL
YOU USED TO BE,
BECAUSE I WITHDREW
THAT PIECE OF YOUR HEART?
HAVE YOU SHUT OUT ALL YOUR
OTHER EMOTIONS BECAUSE OF THAT?
IF THAT'S TRUE, THEN FINE.
IF YOU'RE GOING TO LOVE
SOMEONE ELSE,
BETTER FOR YOU NOT TO LOVE
ANYONE.
IT'S YOUR FAULT, YOU KNOW.
YOU WOULDN'T SO MUCH
AS LOOK AT ME
WHEN I LOVE YOU SO MUCH.
NO. YOU'RE NOT THE ONE TO BLAME.
THAT'S RIGHT.
IF YOU HADN'T BEGUN
TO REGAIN YOUR HEART,
EVERYTHING WOULD'VE PROGRESSED
LIKE IT SHOULD HAVE.
I WOULDN'T HAVE REMEMBERED
THAT I...
THAT I WAS REALLY A CROW.
IT'S ALL THE FAULT
OF THAT NUISANCE.
MM, PESTS LIKE THAT...
THE SOONER WE'RE RID OF HER,
THE BETTER FOR US.
A SINGLE PRINCE HAS NO NEED
OF TWO PRINCESSES.
RIGHT, HERR DROSSELMEYER?
-WHAT? IMPOSSIBLE!
DID I JUST HEAR HER CALL
MY NAME?
-YOU'RE WATCHING
FROM SOMEWHERE, YES?
-AH!
YOU HAVE GUTS TO CALL ON ME.
-GUTS ENOUGH TO OFFER YOU
THE BEST STORY EVER.
-WHAT? REALLY?
-THE BEST OF STORIES DEMANDS
THE BEST OF ENDINGS.
AND FOR THAT,
I NEED A WORTHY STAGE.
-HMM. YOU'RE RIGHT.
AND I HAVE A STAGE
I'VE BEEN SAVING --
A LAKE THAT NO ONE HAS VISITED
IN 200 YEARS.
DO ALLOW ME TO SHOW YOU THE WAY.
[ CHUCKLES ]
-MYTHO!
HE'S NOT HERE EITHER.
HE'S NOT AROUND.
-OF COURSE HE IS.
-HMM?
-IT'S JUST THAT WE HAVEN'T
BEEN ABLE TO FIND HIM.
-HMM. OH!
THE WEAPON ROOM!
-HUH?
-HE MIGHT BE DANCING THERE
RIGHT NOW, HUH?
-AND WHY IS THAT?
-HUH? BECAUSE MYTHO LOVES
TO DANCE, AND THAT'S WHERE...
-I DON'T THINK HE'LL BE THERE.
-BUT -- BUT THE LAST TIME
HE WAS TAKEN,
HE WAS BACK BEFORE WE KNEW IT,
RIGHT?
SO I THOUGHT IT MIGHT BE
THE SAME THIS TIME.
BESIDES, I CAN'T THINK
OF ANYWHERE ELSE.
-WE CAN CHECK IT OUT.
WE'VE NOTHING TO LOSE.
-HUH? OH, WAIT FOR ME!
[ DOOR OPENS ]
[ DOOR CLOSES ]
-THE SCHOOL SURE IS QUIET
ON SUNDAYS.
-I GUESS.
-[ GASPS ]
OH! IS THAT MYTHO?
[ TCHAIKOVSKY'S "DANCE OF
THE SUGAR PLUM FAIRY" PLAYING ]
[ SONGS STOPS ]
-OH!
-HUH? HUH?!
[ GROWLING ]
-[ Whispers ] HEY.
-HUH?
-HE CAN SEE YOU.
-WHAT? WHERE? WHAT?
WHAT?
-[ GROWLING ]
[ HISSES ]
[ CONTINUES GROWLING ]
[ YOWLS]
[ BARKS ]
-HUH?
-[ GASPS ] HOW DARES TO INTRUDE
UPON MY SUNDAY PRACTICE?
-OH!
-OH, MISS DUCK!
THIS TIME I WILL PUNISH YOU FOR
DISTURBING MY TIRELESS EFFORT!
I WILL HAVE YOU MARRY ME
RIGHT NOW!
-I'M SO SORRY! [ GROANS ]
-[ SNARLING ]
-WHAT WERE YOU DOING?
-BUT...BUT...
-[ GASPS ]
-[ Whimpers ]
-HELLO THERE.
-MYTHO? HUH?
SO MYTHO'S OKAY.
THANK GOODNESS HE'S --
-WAIT.
-HUH?
-YOU KNOW THE STORY OF
"THE PRINCE AND THE RAVEN"?
IT'S A TALE OF A BRAVE PRINCE
WHO BATTLES A MONSTER RAVEN.
-[ GASPS ]
-THERE WAS A KNIGHT
WHOM THE PRINCE TRUSTED,
BUT THIS SAME KNIGHT
WAS TORN IN TWO
BY THE CLAWS OF THE RAVEN,
WITHOUT THE KNIGHT EVEN LANDING
A SINGLE BLOW WITH HIS SWORD.
A USELESS WRETCH WHO COULD ONLY
TALK OF PROTECTION.
-UM...
-THAT'S WHY THE PRINCE SUFFERED
SUCH HARDSHIP.
THE RAVEN HAD LEAPT
OUT OF THE STORY.
ALONE HE PURSUED IT,
AND ALONE HE SEALED IT AWAY.
OF HIS OWN WILL,
HE USED A FORBIDDEN POWER.
THAT'S RIGHT.
THE PRINCE DREW HIS SWORD
AND TOOK HIS VERY OWN HEART
OUT OF HIS BODY.
-WHAT?
HOW? HE TOOK HIS --
HE TOOK IT OUT HIMSELF?
-OH, IT'S TRUE.
-WHAT? RUE?
-[ CHUCKLES ] YOU DON'T KNOW
ANYTHING, DO YOU, DUCK?
WHAT DO YOU KNOW ABOUT
PRINCESS TUTU?
-PRINCESS TUTU? NOTHING!
I MEAN, I DON'T KNOW!
-YOU SEE,
IN "THE PRINCE AND THE RAVEN,"
PRINCESS TUTU IS ONLY PRESENTED
IN A FEW SENTENCES --
A MISERABLE EXISTENCE WHICH NONE
OF THE CHARACTERS OF THE STORY
WANTED TO TAKE ON.
AN INSIGNIFICANT EXISTENCE
WHICH EVEN THE STORY LEFT
BY THE WAYSIDE.
SOMEONE WHO COULD NEVER HOPE
TO CATCH THE PRINCE'S EYE,
A LITTLE ADDED FLOURISH.
OH, POOR THING!
-BUT, RUE, WHY ARE YOU
TELLING ME THIS STORY NOW?
-[ LAUGHS ] SO YOU STILL HAVEN'T
FIGURED IT OUT?
RUE DOESN'T EVEN REALLY EXIST.
[ RAVEN CAWS ]
-[ GASPS ]
-WHAT?
-NOW THEN, YOU HAVE FINALLY
FIGURED IT OUT, PRINCESS TUTU.
-PRINCESS...KRAEHE?
NO WAY! YOU CAN'T BE,
'CAUSE YOU'RE MY FRIEND!
WE USED TO CHAT TOGETHER
AND DANCE TOGETHER AND --
-COME ON. KNOCK IT OFF.
-THAT'S TRUE.
BUT THE TIME HAS COME TO PUT
AN END TO ALL THAT FOOLISHNESS.
[ WIND GUSTING ]
-RUE, PLEASE!
-I ONLY CAME
TO RETRIEVE SOMETHING
THE PRINCE LEFT BEHIND,
SO I'LL TAKE MY LEAVE NOW.
-LEFT BEHIND?
-IT IS NOT SOMETHING
FOR A MERE FAILURE OF A KNIGHT
TO HAVE IN HIS CUSTODY.
-THE PRINCE'S SWORD.
BUT WHEN DID SHE GET...
-RUE, NO!
-HURRY UP AND COME RESCUE
THE PRINCE!
[ WIND STOPS ]
-[ LAUGHS ]
-UH...
♪
-OH! MISS EDEL.
-MISS EDEL!
-WATER IS DRAWN TO FIRE,
FIRE TO DARKNESS,
DARKNESS TO SILENCE.
COME. LET US GO.
-UH, WHERE?
-TO WHERE YOU MUST GO.
-[ Whimpers ]
[ TCHAIKOVSKY'S "MARCH" FROM
"THE NUTCRACKER SUITE" PLAYING ]
[ HORSE WHINNIES IN DISTANCE ]
-THIS PLACE...UH, MISS EDEL?
-IT'S LOCKED.
-YOU CAN GO TO WHERE THE PRINCE
AND KRAEHE ARE FROM HERE.
-AN ENTRANCE? HERE?
-GO ON.
-THANKS A LOT, MISS EDEL,
FOR ALWAYS BEING SO KIND TO ME.
-THIS IS NOT KINDNESS.
-HUH?
-PUPPETS FOLLOW
THE PULL OF THEIR STRINGS.
-PUPPETS?
-YES. I AM A PUPPET.
I POSSESS NEITHER FEELINGS
NOR A HEARTBEAT.
-BUT, MISS EDEL, YOU'VE TAUGHT
ME ALL SORTS OF THINGS,
AND YOU'VE BEEN SO FRIENDLY.
THAT'S RIGHT.
I THINK OF YOU LIKE A...
-YOU THINK OF ME LIKE THAT
BECAUSE THAT WAS THE ROLE
I WAS APPOINTED.
-[ Whimpers ]
-MY ORDERS END HERE.
NOW GO ON, DUCK.
-WHOSE ORDERS ARE THAT?
-[ CHUCKLES ]
-MISS EDEL...
-NOW GO ON...
-[ Whimpers ]
-DUCK.
-MISS EDEL,
THANKS A LOT. WE'LL GO NOW.
-DUCK...
-[ GASPS ]
HUH?
-SUCH A WARM FACE.
SUCH SOFT SKIN.
-MISS EDEL, I...
-NOW YOU MUST HURRY.
-OKAY. LET'S GO.
-MM-HMM.
[ SIGHS ]
-GOOD GRIEF.
USE A PUPPET TOO LONG,
THEY START GETTING ATTACHED
TO THINGS OTHER THAN STRINGS,
THINGS LIKE PEOPLE'S FEELINGS.
DON'T YOU FORGET.
YOUR ROLE IS TO ADD A GLOW
TO THE STORY IN MY PLACE.
THAT'S ABOUT ALL YOU'RE CAPABLE
OF DOING ANYHOW.
NOT KNOWING YOUR PLACE
IN THE WORLD
IS DANGEROUS, YOU KNOW.
[ FOOTSTEPS DESCEND ]
[ WATER DRIPPING ]
-SCARY. AAH!
-IDIOT. WALK TOWARDS THE MIDDLE.
YOU'RE ALREADY CARELESS ENOUGH
AS IT IS.
-HUH?
HMM.
WOW! THIS PLACE IS
KINDA INCREDIBLE!
OH!
[THUD ]
-OKAY. OKAY. EYES FORWARD!
OH!
[ THUD ]
-WHOA!
-[ PANTING ]
-UM, YOU REALLY ARE
PRINCESS TUTU, AREN'T YOU?
-[ GROANS ]
YEAH. WHAT OF IT?
-I THOUGHT PRINCESS TUTU WAS
MORE, UH...YOU KNOW.
-HUH?
-NEVER MIND.
-SAY, FAKIR?
-WHAT IS IT?
-N-NOTHING. NEVER MIND.
-WHAT THE HECK?
IF YOU DIDN'T WANNA SAY IT,
JUST KEEP YOUR MOUTH SHUT.
-OH! NO, IT'S NOT LIKE THAT.
BUT JUST SO YOU KNOW,
I DON'T THINK YOU'RE NO GOOD
AS A KNIGHT OR ANYTHING.
-WHAT ARE YOU GETTING AT?
-I'M NOT REALLY TRYING
TO GET AT ANYTHING.
IT'S JUST, I DIDN'T THINK
YOU WERE VERY NICE
WHEN WE FIRST MET,
BUT NOW I FEEL LIKE
I KNOW YOU A LITTLE BETTER.
-I'LL SAY THIS RIGHT NOW.
I HAVE NO INTENTION
OF COOPERATING WITH YOU.
I'LL HELP MYTHO IN MY OWN WAY.
END OF STORY.
-MM.
I KNOW THAT.
WOW. YOU KNOW?
-HMM?
-[ CHUCKLES ] NEVER MIND.
IT'S NOTHING.
-WHAT IS YOUR PROBLEM?
QUIT STOPPING IN THE MIDDLE
OF YOUR SENTENCES.
-[ Whimpers ]
WELL, THE TRUTH IS, THAT I NEVER
THOUGHT ABOUT THINGS LIKE,
WHAT DO I LIKE ABOUT MYTHO?
-MM.
-[ Whimpers ]
[ GRUNTS ]
THE FIRST TIME I SAW MYTHO,
IT WAS MOSTLY ME JUST THINKING
HE WAS HANDSOME.
BUT WHEN I LOOKED CLOSER,
HIS EYES LOOKED SO LONELY,
AND I THOUGHT
IF I BECAUSE PRINCESS TUTU,
THEN MAYBE I COULD
DO SOMETHING FOR HIM.
AT THE START, THAT'S ALL
THERE REALLY WAS TO IT.
BUT NOW, I...
[ THUD IN DISTANCE ]
[ RAVENS CAWING ]
-[ GRUNTS ]
-WHOA!
[ BLADE ZINGS ]
-DAMN!
-[ GRUNTS ] FAKIR!
-RUN! [ GRUNTING ]
[ RAVENS CAWING ]
-AAH! UHH!
HEY! I'M --
-IDIOT!
-AAH!
[ RAVENS CONTINUE CAWING ]
[ WATER DRIPS ]
-[ GRUNTS ]
-[ GRUNTS ] SORRY.
ARE YOU HURT AT ALL?
-IT'S A MIRACLE I'M NOT.
WHAT IS THIS PLACE?
I GUESS WE'LL JUST HAVE TO
CLIMB BACK UP.
-UH...OH!
[ Thinking ] WE MIGHT BE ABLE
TO GET OUT THROUGH THE WATER.
I COULD GO CHECK IT OUT
IF I BECAME A BIRD, BUT...
-IT'S COVERED IN MOSS.
I DOUBT WE CAN CLIMB IT.
DAMN.
[ BOOT SCRAPES ]
-SINCE IT'S FAKIR...
FAKIR?
-WHAT IS IT?
-ONE TIME, WHEN I HAD LOST
THIS NECKLACE,
YOU HELD ON TO IT FOR ME.
REMEMBER, FAKIR?
-UH-HUH. WHAT ABOUT IT?
-WOULD YOU HOLD ON TO IT AGAIN?
-WHAT THE HECK
IS THIS ALL ABOUT?
-MM.
HERE.
-HUH?
[ TINKLING ]
-WHAT WAS THAT?
WHERE DID SHE GO?
[ FABRIC RUSTLING ]
-QUACK!
-A DUCK?
-QUACK.
-SHE JUST...
SO THEN THIS WASN'T A PENDANT
FOR HER TO BECOME TUTU?
IT CAN'T BE THAT DUCK.
SORRY YOU'VE CAUGHT ME
AT A BAD MOMENT.
[ Muffled shout ]
[ GRUNTS ]
[ GROANS ]
-BUT JUST SO YOU KNOW,
I DON'T THINK YOU'RE NO GOOD
AS A KNIGHT OR ANYTHING.
-SHE SAW...ME CRYING.
NO WAY.
SHE ISN'T DROWNING NOW, IS SHE?
CAN DUCKS EVEN DROWN, THOUGH?
KNOWING HER, SHE MIGHT.
[ WATER DRIPPING ]
-IDIOT!
-QUACK!
QUACK, QUACK, QUACK!
QUACK QUACK! QUACK QUACK QUACK!
QUACK! QUACK QUACK QUACK QUACK!
-WHAT DID YOU...
WHY DID YOU NOT TELL ME?!
YOU SHOULDN'T HIDE THINGS
LIKE THAT!
-QUACK?
-QUIT PLAYING DIRTY, YOU...
-[ GRUNTS ] QUACK!
QUACK QUACK, QUACK QUACK, QUACK!
[ TINKLING ]
-[ GASPS ]
-[ GRUNTS ] YOU SAY THAT,
BUT IT'S NOT LIKE I REVEALED IT
TO YOU BECAUSE I WANTED TO!
IT'S JUST EASIER WHEN I'M A BIRD
TO CHECK SMALL...[ Whimpers ]
-MM.
-UH...[ Whimpers ]
OH! [ GIGGLES ]
[ WATER SPLASHES ]
-YOU SAW?
-NO.
MORE IMPORTANTLY,
WHAT DID YOU SEE?!
SHOULDN'T YOU BE
BRINGING THAT UP FIRST?!
-HOW CAN I WHEN --
-DON'T STAND!
-WE CAN MAKE IT TO THE OTHER
SIDE THROUGH THE WATER.
THE WATER DOWN THAT WAY
SMELLS DIFFERENT,
SO THERE'S PROBABLY A LAKE
UP AHEAD.
SEE? IT LOOKS LIKE IT GOES DEEP.
THAT'S PROBABLY WHERE MYTHO IS.
WERE YOU OKAY BACK THERE, FAKIR?
-[ CHUCKLES ]
-HUH? WHAT IS IT?
-A DUCK IS PRINCESS TUTU, HUH?
-WHAT?
-I HAVE SOMETHING
YOU'LL WANT TO HEAR.
BACK WHEN I WAS STILL A BRAT,
WHEN I WAS READING "THE PRINCE
AND THE RAVEN" TO MYTHO,
THE THING THAT HE SHOWED
THE STRONGEST INTEREST IN
WAS NEITHER WHAT HAPPENED
TO HIMSELF NOR THE RAVEN,
BUT WHAT HAPPENED TO TUTU,
ABOUT WHOM ONLY A LITTLE
WAS ACTUALLY WRITTEN.
HE WANTED TO HEAR
OVER AND OVER AGAIN
THE PART WHERE TUTU TURNS
INTO A SPECK OF LIGHT
AND THEN VANISHES.
HIS SUDDEN DESIRE
TO REGAIN HIS HEART
MOST LIKELY STEMS FROM
TUTU'S ROLE IN RETURNING IT.
-BUT...THEY WERE SAYING
MYTHO TOOK HIS HEART OUT
HIMSELF.
-THAT'S THE KIND OF GUY HE IS.
WELL, YOU SEE,
PROTECTING THE SMALL
AND THE WEAK,
THAT IS MYTHO'S
SINGLE GREATEST DESIRE.
AND TO FULFILL THAT, HE'LL CAST
OFF ANY REGARD FOR HIMSELF.
EVEN THE LOSS OF HIS HEART
COULDN'T TEAR THAT OUT OF HIM.
THAT'S MYTHO.
-MM.
[ WATER DRIPS ]
-LET'S GO.
-RIGHT.
-FINALLY, HE'S COME.
I'VE TIRED OF WAITING.
-[ GRUNTING ] OH!
-HUH?
-OH! MYTHO!
[ WIND GUSTING ]
-WELCOME TO THE STAGE
I'VE BEEN SAVING.
NOW TELL ME THE BEST STORY
THAT WAS EVER TOLD!
TELL IT TO ME WITH NO REGARD
FOR YOUR LIVES!
[ LAUGHS EVILLY ]
[ TINKLING ]
-PLEASE,
STOP THIS MALEVOLENCE NOW!
-AGREED.
LET US PUT AN END TO IT.
-[ Whimpers ]
-THE PRINCE'S FEELING OF LOVE
IS RIGHT HERE.
THE HEART THAT LOVES PEOPLE,
THAT LOVES ALL THE WORLD,
YET BELONGS TO NO ONE.
AND I WONDER, YOU OR ME --
WHICH ONE OF US WILL IT CHOOSE?
WHOSE WORDS WILL IT BE DRAWN TO
ONCE WE'VE BOTH
LAID OUR HEARTS BARE?
IF THE SHARD CHOOSES YOU,
I'LL RETURN IT AND THE PRINCE.
SO THEN,
WHY DON'T YOU SPEAK TO IT
OF WHAT BURNS IN YOUR HEART?
WELL, PRINCESS TUTU?
-[ LAUGHING EVILLY ]
[ RITSUKO OKAZAKI'S "ALTHOUGH
MY LOVE IS SMALL" PLAYING ]
-♪ YUME MIRU ♪
♪ YOU NI ♪
♪ KOI O SHITA NO ♪
♪ FUKURAMU ♪
♪ KOKORO GA FUKURAMU NO YO ♪
♪ IKITERUTTE SUTEKI
NA KOTO TO OMOTTA ♪
♪ ASU GA MACHI DOOSHII ♪
♪ MM ♪
♪ ANATA NO CHIKARA NI NARITAI
NO DONNA TOKI NI MO WATASHI ♪
♪ MATTE MATTE
KURENAI HASHITTE ♪
♪ HASHITTE IKU NO YO ♪
♪ KAZE MO AMAGUMO
MO OIKOSHITE ♪
♪ WATASHI DAKE
NO TSUBASA HABATAITE ♪
-BUT WHY DO WE HAVE TO FIGHT
EACH OTHER THIS WAY?
BECAUSE WE BOTH --
-ULTIMATELY,
YOU WERE ONLY BORROWING
THE POWER OF PRINCESS TUTU.
YOU ARE MERELY A SHAM
OF A PRINCESS, HEY, DUCK.
-YOU ALONE AND NOBODY ELSE
COULD ACCEPT PRINCESS TUTU'S
FATE SO SMILINGLY.
-YOU ARE MY TRUE PRINCESS.
-YES, I AM
YOUR ONE TRUE PRINCESS.
-THE REAL ME IS JUST A DUCK
WITH NO POWERS OF MY OWN.
BUT IF I HAVE YOU,
I CAN TRANSFORM!
-ALL YOU CHILDREN
WHO LOVE STORIES,
COME GATHER 'ROUND.
[ LAUGHS EVILLY ]