-ONCE UPON A TIME,
THERE WAS A CHILD.
FOR THE CHILD, THE WORLD WAS
FILLED WITH WONDER.
"HOW?" "WHY?"
"HOW COME?"
WHEN ONE MYSTERY WAS SOLVED,
TWO NEW MYSTERIES WOULD ARISE.
WHEN TWO MYSTERIES WERE SOLVED,
FOUR NEW MYSTERIES WOULD ARISE.
WHEN FOUR MYSTERIES WERE SOLVED,
COUNTLESS MYSTERIES APPEARED.
IN TIME, THE CHILD CAME TO BE
CONSUMED BY THESE MYSTERIES.
[ RITSUKO OKAZAKI'S
"MORNING GRACE" PLAYS ]
-[ SINGING IN JAPANESE ]
[ SINGING CONTINUES ]
[ TCHAIKOVSKY'S "FINAL
WALTZ AND APOTHEOSIS" FROM
"THE NUTCRACKER" PLAYS ]
-NO. STOP.
PLEASE, DON'T COME NEAR ME.
TUTU.
AAH! AAAAAAH!
-NO, I DIDN'T MEAN FOR HIM
TO SUFFER LIKE THAT,
NOT KNOWING ABOUT FEELINGS,
LIKE WHAT IT WAS LIKE
TO BE HAPPY OR IN LOVE!
I JUST THOUGHT IT WAS SAD,
AND THAT'S WHY! THAT'S WHY!
-QUACK! QUACK! QUACK! QUACK!
QUACK! QUACK!
-AAAAAH!
-QUACK! QUACK! QUACK! QUACK!
QUACK! QUACK! QUACK!
[ BIRDS CHIRPING ]
-[ Crying ] I DIDN'T MEAN IT
TO BE LIKE THIS.
[ SOBBING ]
-DUCK, WE'RE LEAVING!
-IF YOU DON'T HURRY,
YOU'LL GO BACK TO BEING
PROBATIONARY, DUCK!
-YEAH, YEAH, I HEAR YOU.
OH, MAN.
MYTHO HASN'T BEEN TO CLASS
SINCE THEN.
NOW COME HERE.
-WHAT'S WRONG? WHAT SCARES YOU?
-I'M AFRAID OF PRINCESS TUTU.
-[ GASPING ]
IT'S ALL MY FAULT.
[ WHIMPERS ]
[ CRIES ]
-I WONDER IF MYTHO'S ALL RIGHT.
-[ Mexican accent ] IT'S
BEEN A WEEK SINCE MYTHO
STOPPING COMING TO CLASS.
-FAKIR, TOO.
-WHAT THE HECK
ARE THEY THINKING?
-WELL, IT'S NOT LIKE
YOU CAN EVER TELL
WHAT MYTHO'S THINKING ANYWAY.
[ LAUGHTER ]
-EVERYONE DID EXCEPTIONALLY WELL
ON THE REPORT ON
"SLEEPING BEAUTY"
BY THE ELEKI TROUPE THE OTHER
DAY, ESPECIALLY MISS RUE.
BRILLIANTLY INSIGHTFUL.
I EXPECTED NO LESS.
-THANK YOU VERY MUCH.
-AND THEN WE COME TO WHAT SEEMS
TO BE MISS DUCK'S REPORT.
-OOH!
-"IT WAS REALLY GREAT.
THE END."
[ BOTH GASP ]
BRILLIANTLY SUCCINCT.
I EXPECTED NO LESS.
-THANK YOU VERY MUCH.
[ FLIP! ]
-IT'S SARCASM.
-YES, MR. CAT.
-[ SIGHING ]
-AT THIS RATE, I'LL HAVE TO DROP
YOU DOWN TO PROBATION AGAIN
OR...HAVE YOU MARRY --
-THAT'S FINE.
-[ GASPS ]
-NO!
-IT'S FINE?
YOU MEAN BEING DROPPED
TO PROBATION?
OR ABOUT M-M-M--
-OH, NO! A FEVER!
-AND GOOSE BUMPS, TOO!
-UH, WE NEED A DOCTOR!
-PLEASE EXCUSE US!
[ WHIP! ]
-HOLD IT RIGHT THERE!
[ SCREECH! ]
-[ GASPS ]
-IF IT IS YOUR WISH TO MARRY ME,
LET US MEET AFTER SCHOOL.
THE PIZZA --
[ DOOR CLOSES ]
HUH?
OHH.
[ YOWLS ]
[ WINDOW CREAKS ]
[ SOFT INSTRUMENTAL MUSIC
PLAYING ]
-WHAT'S WRONG?
YOU'VE BEEN KIND OF DOWN LATELY.
-IT MAKES ME SAD TO SEE YOU
IN SUCH A STATE.
-[ WHIMPERS ]
-BUT, HEY,
NO MATTER WHAT HAPPENS,
YOU ALWAYS FORGET ABOUT IT
RIGHT AWAY AND CHEER UP AGAIN.
-YEAH, LIKE A BIRD.
[ TONK! ]
-UGH.
-HUH? COME ON, NOW!
WHAT'S WRONG? SNAP OUT OF IT!
-WELL, IT'S YOUR FAULT.
-HEY!
-I DON'T KNOW.
I DON'T GET IT ANYMORE.
-HUH?
-ABOUT WHAT?
-DON'T WORRY.
YOU NEVER GOT ANY OF THE STUFF
IN CLASS ANYWAY, REMEMBER?
-NOT LIKE THAT.
THINGS LIKE,
WHAT DO I WANT TO DO?
JUST EVERYTHING.
[ BOTH GASP ]
-THAT SOUNDS PRETTY HEAVY.
-COULD IT BE...
-BECAUSE MYTHO HASN'T BEEN
TO CLASSES?
-[ WHIMPERING ]
-I KNEW IT.
-AT TIMES LIKE THIS, WHY DON'T
YOU GO TO THE PRODDING BRIDGE?
-THE PLOTTING BRIDGE?
-THE PRODDING BRIDGE.
YOU DON'T KNOW IT?
IT'S THE OLD BRIDGE
OVER THE RIVER TO THE NORTH.
-WHEN YOU STAND ON THAT BRIDGE
AND TALK ABOUT
WHAT'S BUGGING YOU,
AND OUT OF NOWHERE, A VOICE
COMES AND STARTS ASKING,
"WHY? HOW COME?"
-UH, A GHOST STORY?
-[ Creepy voice ]
NO GHOSTS HERE.
-[ GASPS ]
-ONLY QUESTION AFTER QUESTION
HITTING YOU TILL YOU SORT OUT
HOW YOU FEEL.
-BUT WHY'S YOUR VOICE SO CREEPY?
-[ Creepy voice ] ALTHOUGH
THAT'S NOT ALL, YOU KNOW.
-WHAT?
-THAT'S RIGHT.
IF YOU TAKE TOO LONG
TO ANSWER...
-WHAT?
-THE RIVER SWALLOWS YOU UP
AND TAKES YOU UNDER!
[ Normal voice ]
NAH, JUST KIDDING.
-THOUGH THERE IS A LEGEND
LIKE THAT.
-IT'S AN OLD, OLD STORY.
-BUT WHAT ABOUT NOW?
-[ Creepy voices ] WHO KNOWS?
MAYBE IT WAS TRUE THEN.
BUT I DOUBT IT IS NOW!
-AAH!
THEN JUST TALK NORMAL, HUH?
-[ Normal voice ]
BUT THERE'S SEVERAL PEOPLE
WHO SAY THEY REALLY HEARD
VOICES.
-HUH?
-[ Normal voice ]
WELL, AS THEY SAY,
IT DOESN'T HURT TO TRY.
-YEAH! I'M GONNA GO!
-NOW, THAT'S OUR DUCK.
-ALL RIGHT.
-[ Creepy voices ]
GOT TO BE CAREFUL!
-[ SHRIEKS ]
[ BELL TOLLING ]
NOTHING TO BE SCARED OF.
I JUST GOT TO MAKE SURE
I KNOW WHAT I SHOULD DO.
I'LL MAKE SURE I...
MAKE SURE I WHAT?
[ GASPS ]
-HMM?
[ FLUTTER! ]
-UH...[ CHUCKLES NERVOUSLY ]
SO, ARE YOU...HERE
FOR THE PLOTTING BRIDGE?
IT'S THE PRODDING BRIDGE.
-OH, RIGHT!
SO, EVEN YOU HAVE THINGS
YOU'RE NOT SURE ABOUT?
-HUH?
-IS IT ABOUT MYTHO?
-[ SIGHS ]
THAT'S WHY I CAME HERE,
BUT I CHANGED MY MIND.
-OH.
WELL, I'M SURE HE'LL BE COMING
TO SCHOOL AGAIN SOON.
-AND WHY DO YOU THINK THAT?
[ TINK! ]
-JUST...A FEELING.
I'M SORRY FOR SAYING THINGS
AND STUFF.
-MM. SEE YOU LATER.
-UH...
UH, HEY, RUE?
-HMM?
-RUE, SO, YOU KNOW THAT MYTHO
DOESN'T HAVE A HEART, DON'T YOU?
-UH...OF COURSE.
-OKAY, SO, DON'T YOU THINK IT'D
BE BETTER IF HE HAD A HEART?
-[ GASPS ]
[ HUM! ]
IT DOESN'T MATTER.
-HUH?
-THE ONLY ONE I'VE EVER
HAD EYES FOR IS MYTHO.
WHETHER OR NOT HE HAS A HEART
DOES NOT IN ANY WAY
CHANGE THE SIMPLE FACT
THAT I LOVE HIM.
-[ GASPS ]
-I WILL CONTINUE TO LOVE HIM.
I'M STILL FAR FROM
HAVING LOVED HIM ENOUGH.
-[ Thinking ]
RUE SAID SHE LOVES MYTHO.
BUT I --
[ SPARKLE! ]
I'M JUST A BIRD,
SO SOMETHING LIKE THAT...
-[ GASPING ]
AAH!
-SNAP OUT OF IT, MYTHO.
-[ BREATHING HEAVILY ]
-CALM DOWN.
-[ GASPS ]
-WHAT IS IT?
-FAKIR, I HAD A DREAM.
THERE WAS A GIGANTIC BLACK
BEING, AND IT WAS --
-DON'T WORRY.
-WHO WAS THAT?
-DON'T TROUBLE YOURSELF.
YOU DON'T NEED TO KNOW ANYTHING.
GOT IT?
-WHERE'S TUTU?
-RELAX.
NOBODY KNOWS WE'RE HERE.
[ POURING DRINK ]
-I CAN'T SEE TUTU?
-[ SCOFFS ] THAT'S RIGHT.
IF YOU STAY IN HERE, YOU'LL
EVENTUALLY FORGET EVERYTHING.
YOU WON'T BE LED ASTRAY BY
THOSE INANE EMOTIONS, EITHER.
THAT'S WHAT'S BEST FOR YOU.
-I WANT TO MAKE SURE,
BUT BOTH RUE AND FAKIR SAY
HE DOESN'T NEED A HEART.
PLUS, MYTHO'S SUFFERING.
WHAT IS THERE TO MAKE SURE THEN?
[ DING! ]
[ GASPS ] A HEART SHARD!
AW.
BEING PRINCESS TUTU
IS MEANINGLESS.
I COULD QUIT AND...
-SHE WOULDN'T!
-...IF I RETURN THIS, BUT THEN
I'D GO BACK TO BEING A BIRD.
WHAT IF I JUST STAYED A GIRL?
WOULD THAT BE DISHONEST?
IT WOULD, WOULDN'T IT?
I BETTER JUST END THIS NOW.
-DAMN IT ALL!
THE STORY WILL BE LEFT HANGING
AT THIS RATE.
NO, NO, NO, NO, NO!
I REFUSE TO LET EVERYTHING END
HERE.
NO CHARACTER IN A STORY
WOULD EVER SAY
THEY'RE GOING TO END THINGS
IN A SPOT LIKE THIS.
IT'S ABSOLUTELY UNHEARD OF!
I SWEAR, REALITY IS SO --
WELL, SINCE IT'S COME TO THIS,
I HAVE NO CHOICE BUT TO USE THIS
PASSAGEWAY OF TIME ONCE AGAIN,
THOUGH IT'S SO OLD,
WHO KNOWS HOW MANY MORE TIMES
I'LL BE ABLE TO USE IT?
[ WATER BURBLING ]
-THERE WAS NOTHING I COULD DO.
RIGHT FROM THE START,
I JUST FELL IN LOVE
AND BELIEVED WHAT I WANTED TO.
[ GASPS ]
[ TEAR DRIPS ]
UH...HUH?
OH.
[ DOOR OPENS, CREAKS ]
[ GASPS ]
[ DRAMATIC MUSIC PLAYS ]
-LONG TIME, NO SEE, LITTLE DUCK.
-[ GASPS ]
-FOR SHAME.
HAVE YOU FORGOTTEN?
IT IS I, DROSSELMEYER.
-BUT YOU'RE --
YOU'RE SUPPOSED TO BE --
I MEAN,
I WAS TOLD THAT YOU WERE DEAD.
-YES, I AM DEAD,
COMPLETELY DEAD,
WHICH IS WHY I'M LIMITED
TO MEET YOU IN THIS WAY.
I CAME ALL THIS WAY TO CONVINCE
YOU OF THE UTTER FOOLISHNESS
OF QUITTING YOUR VOCATION
AS PRINCESS TUTU.
NOW YOU HAVE TO GO RESTORE
THE PRINCE'S HEART TO HIM.
-BUT ALL I'VE GOTTEN FOR HIM
IS FEAR AND TEARS.
-[ LAUGHS EVILLY ]
YES, HOW DELIGHTFUL.
OH, UM --
-[ GASPS ]
-[ STAMMERS ]
NOW, LISTEN, IF YOU GO BACK
TO BEING A DUCK,
YOU'LL NEVER GET TO SEE
THE PRINCE AGAIN.
-MR. DROSSELMEYER?
-WHAT IS IT?
-WHY'D YOU GIVE ME THE CHANCE
TO BE PRINCESS TUTU?
-WELL, THAT'S EASY.
-HUH?
-[ CHUCKLES ]
BECAUSE IT WOULD BE FUN.
-WHAT DO YOU MEAN?
-[ STAMMERS ]
NO, WH-WHAT I MEAN IS,
YOU'RE THE ONLY ONE WHO CAN.
-ONLY I CAN?
-THAT'S RIGHT.
ALTHOUGH SHE RISKED EVERYTHING
FOR HER PRINCE,
PRINCESS TUTU IS FATED NEVER
TO BE UNITED WITH HIM.
-UH --
-OH, HOW CRUEL!
WHAT A THANKLESS ROLE!
NO ONE WANTS TO BE HER.
[ LAUGHS EVILLY ]
-ON TOP OF THAT,
THE PRINCE JUST HATES ME NOW.
-YES. IT'S TRULY DELIGHTFUL.
-[ WHIMPERS ]
-YOU SEE, DON'T YOU,
IF YOU DO IT, WHO WILL?
[ ZAP! ]
-AAH! NO! WAIT!
-I DON'T CARE!
-OHH! WHAT ARE YOU THINKING?!
[ SPARKLE! ]
-[ WHIMPERS ]
-NO! DON'T!
-QUACK! QUACK! QUACK!
QUACK! QUACK!
-NOT GOOD!
I LEAVE IT TO YOU.
[ DOOR CREAKS ]
[ WATER BURBLING ]
-[ HUMMING MENDELSSOHN'S
"WEDDING MARCH" ]
-PRINCESS TUTU.
WHAT IS THIS FEELING THAT I HAVE
WHEN I THINK ABOUT HER?
FEAR WAS WHAT I FELT
IN THE DREAM, BUT THIS IS --
[ THUD ]
WHO'S THERE?
FAKIR?
TUTU?
[ WATER BURBLING ]
-WHO'S TUTU?
WHAT KIND OF PERSON IS SHE?
-SOMEONE I FEAR.
-YOU FEAR HER, YET YOU SEEK HER.
HOW STRANGE. WHY?
-I DON'T REALLY KNOW.
-WHY DO YOU FEAR HER?
-SHE'S BEEN RESTORING MY HEART
TO ME.
-YOU DON'T HAVE A HEART.
-NO.
-IS IT BETTER NOT TO?
-YES.
-WHY?
-I DON'T KNOW.
-QUACK.
AT LEAST I WON'T HAVE TO WORRY
ABOUT THINGS
LIKE GETTING DROPPED IN
THE PROBATIONARY CLASS ANYMORE.
[ MUSIC BOX PLAYING ]
[ GASPS ]
MISS EDEL.
-WOULD YOU LIKE TO BUY
SOME GEMS?
A BIRD'S WORLD OR GIRL'S WORLD,
THE FABLED AND THE REAL WORLD,
THE GEM THAT LINKS
YOUR TWO WORLDS.
WILL YOU CUT THAT LINK...
-QUACK.
-...NOW THAT YOU'VE BRIDGED
THE TWO?
-UH...
UH...
QUACK! IT DOESN'T MATTER!
-YOU'RE A STRANGE ONE.
COME WITH ME TO A PLACE
WHERE NONE WILL FOLLOW.
-COME WITH YOU?
-YES.
YOU'RE SO STRANGE.
I WANT TO KNOW MORE ABOUT YOU.
I WANT TO KNOW.
I WANT TO KNOW MORE.
-OKAY, I WILL.
[ UP-TEMPO CLASSICAL MUSIC
PLAYING ]
-QUACK!
MNH! MYTHO!
AAH!
OH, NO!
QUACK!
QUACK. QUACK. QUACK.
[ WINGS FLUTTERING ]
QUACK! [ GASPS ]
[ STRAUSS' "THE BLUE DANUBE"
PLAYING ]
HUH? WHAT IS THIS?
QUACK! I CAN'T CATCH UP TO IT!
WHAT DO I DO?
-SINCE WHEN HAVE YOU NOT HAD
A HEART?
-NO IDEA.
-HOW DID YOU LOSE IT?
-WELL, I...
I-I FEEL AS THOUGH
THERE WAS SOMETHING IMPORTANT
THAT I HAD TO DO.
-WHAT'S THAT?
-I DON'T KNOW.
-I WANT TO KNOW.
DON'T YOU WANT TO KNOW?
-MNH.
-REALLY?
-PROBABLY.
-WHY DON'T YOU WANT TO KNOW?
-IT HURTS
WHEN I TRY TO FIND OUT.
-HOW STRANGE.
YOU AND I ARE VERY ALIKE.
LIKE YOU, I DON'T KNOW
WHAT I AM, EITHER.
BUT YOU AND I ARE THE OPPOSITE.
-WHAT?
-I WANT TO KNOW SO BADLY
THAT IT HURTS.
-COULD IT BE THAT YOU'RE...
-UNH!
THIS IS USELESS.
IF I COULD JUST --
IF I COULD JUST
BECOME PRINCESS TUTU
ONE MORE TIME!
-THAT'S MORE LIKE IT!
AND NOT JUST ONCE,
BUT MANY, MANY MORE TIMES!
[ LAUGHS EVILLY ]
[ SPARKLE! ]
[ SPARKLE! SPARKLE! SPARKLE! ]
[ MUSIC CONTINUES ]
[ SPARKLE! SPARKLE! ]
-[ GASPS ] PRINCESS TUTU?
-PRINCESS TUTU?
THE PERSON YOU'RE AFRAID OF?
-[ WHIMPERING ]
-PLEASE DON'T BE AFRAID.
COME BACK WITH ME.
-YOU'RE PRINCESS TUTU?
-UH...
-WHY DO YOU RESTORE HIS HEART
TO HIM?
-IT'S...
-MM.
-IT'S BECAUSE I THOUGHT
THAT WAS WHAT WAS BEST FOR HIM.
YES, THERE ARE PAINFUL FEELINGS
LIKE SORROW AND LONELINESS,
BUT THERE ARE LOTS
OF WARM FEELINGS, TOO,
LIKE JOY AND LOVE.
I WANTED TO GET THOSE THINGS
BACK FOR HIM.
THAT'S WHY.
BECAUSE I BELIEVED
HE WOULD BE HAPPIER THAT WAY,
BECAUSE I NEVER IMAGINED
HE WOULD SUFFER SO MUCH
ON MY ACCOUNT.
[ CRIES ]
-TUTU.
-[ CRYING ]
-DON'T CRY, TUTU.
I'LL COME BACK WITH YOU.
-[ EXHALES SHARPLY ]
[ MUSIC CONTINUES ]
-YOU'RE AFRAID OF HER,
YET YOU'RE GOING WITH HER?
HOW STRANGE.
-[ GASPS ]
-MYTHO.
[ WATER BURBLING ]
WHERE DID HE GO?
-OH, I, UH -- I'M SORRY,
BUT I'M AFRAID THIS WILL BE
THE LAST TIME.
-HUH?
-I PROMISE TO NEVER APPEAR
BEFORE YOU AGAIN,
SO DON'T WORRY.
-[ EXHALES SHARPLY ]
-UH, WELL, GOODBYE.
-WAIT.
-UH...
[ STRAUSS' "THE BLUE DANUBE"
PLAYING ]
-I UNDERSTAND A LITTLE
OF WHAT I'M FEELING RIGHT NOW.
-WHAT?
-THESE ARE THE FEELINGS
OF LONELINESS...
AND OF SORROW.
I DON'T WANT YOU
TO JUST DISAPPEAR.
-BUT I -- I HAVEN'T BROUGHT YOU
ANYTHING BUT PAIN.
-I DON'T CARE.
-UH...
-EVEN IF IT HURTS,
WHEN I THINK OF YOU,
I CAN FEEL A SMALL LIGHT
BEING KINDLED
AND COMING TO LIFE IN MY HEART.
-SO -- SO CAN I.
-IF YOU WERE TO DISAPPEAR,
I FEEL LIKE THAT LIGHT WOULD BE
SNUFFED OUT AND VANISH WITH YOU.
-OH.
-THAT'S WHAT I FEAR.
-[ GASPS ]
-I WANT YOU TO RESTORE MY HEART,
TUTU.
-[ GASPS ]
-THE THING POSSESSING THIS RIVER
IS MOST LIKELY MY DESIRE
FOR KNOWLEDGE.
RETURN IT TO MY HEART.
-BUT...
-I SEE.
SO, I AM YOU.
-ARE YOU REALLY SURE?
-YES.
[ SPARKLE! ]
[ MUSIC CONTINUES ]
[ SCREECH! ]
[ FLUTTERING ]
[ WIND HOWLING ]
[ BOTH EXHALE SHARPLY ]
-[ GASPS ]
AAH!
[ WIND FADES ]
THE HEART SHARD.
[ GASPS ]
[ FLUTTERING ]
WHO ARE YOU?
-PRINCESS KRAEHE.
-PRINCESS KRAEHE?
-HMM. WHAT IS THIS?
-GIVE IT BACK!
-NO WAY.
-[ GASPS ]
-[ CHUCKLES ]
I WILL GIVE YOU NOTHING.
I WILL LET YOU DO NOTHING.
-WHAT?
-[ LAUGHS ]
[ WIND HOWLING ]
-[ GASPS ]
[ AIR WHOOSHING ]
-[ LAUGHS ]
STAY AWAY FROM THE PRINCE.
[ CHUCKLES ]
WHO -- WHO AM I?
-AAH!
[ WHIMPERS ]
[ WIND FADES ]
MYTHO?
[ GASPS ]
MYTHO!
MYTHO?
-[ GASPS ]
MYTHO.
GET UP! MYTHO!
GET A HOLD OF YOURSELF!
MYTHO? [ GASPS ]
I SEE.
SO, YOU FINALLY MADE
AN APPEARANCE.
-VERY GOOD, VERY GOOD.
THE SPROUTING OF A NEW SEED OF
CALAMITY, THE DEEPENING MYSTERY.
AND TO THE DUCK WHO CHOSE THE
PATH OF SUFFERING AND TRAGEDY
GOES A HEARTY ROUND OF APPLAUSE!
[ LAUGHS EVILLY ]
[ MENDELSSOHN'S "WEDDING MARCH"
PLAYING ]
-[ CHUCKLES ]
[ MEOWING ]
[ SLOW MUSIC PLAYS ]
-[ SINGING IN JAPANESE ]
-CONFESSING YOUR LOVE
AT THE WINDOW?!
DUCK, YOU'RE SO BOLD!
-IT WAS LIKE A REVERSE
"ROMEO AND JULIET"!
-SOMEHOW HE WASN'T LIKE
THE USUAL FAKIR.
-LOOK, MY PRINCE.
THERE'S THE ONE MAKING
YOU SUFFER -- PRINCESS TUTU.
-PRINCESS TUTU,
WHAT DO YOU THINK OF ME?
I WANT TO KNOW.
-I, UH...
I...
-I'LL SET THINGS RIGHT
AND SHATTER YOUR HEART FOR YOU
ONCE AGAIN.
-ALL WHO LOVE STORIES,
GATHER 'ROUND.
[ LAUGHS EVILLY ]