‐ [Narrator] Once upon
a time there was a sad love
that would never be requited.
But that alone does not
give birth to a story.
The man charged with a task
of spinning this tale of love
was no longer of this world.
The story lives on with the
love forever immersed in sorrow.
Having lost its storyteller,
the story is nowZ
wandering in search of its
conclusion.
(soft piano music)
(soft singing in Japanese)
(lively classical music)
(lively classical ballet music)
(gasping in awe)
(girls sighing)
‐ Impressive!
‐ Truly a prodigy!
‐ Will a day come when
I can dance like that too?
‐ Whoa, you finally
got your head straight!
‐ What a wildly whimsical dream!
That's the spirit, Duck!
Ballet is your strong suit!
Better to dream big right?
Then you'll have bigger
failures!
‐ Work hard and things work out!
‐ For normal people!
‐ [Both] Yeah well, for now you
gotta get
out of that probationary class!
‐ [Duck] That's right,
when I'm Princess Tutu
I can dance any dance I want.
But is that me
or someone else?
I'm just a girl in the
probationary class.
Or rather, when you get
down to it, I'm just a duck.
Maybe there's no point in me
practicing.
(panting in effort)
Watch out!
(gasping in horror)
(chimes ringing)
‐ Who are you?
Are you calling to me?
Fakir‐‐
‐ What's with that look?
‐ What look?
‐ What were you thinking?
‐ What?
‐ Just now, what were you
thinking?
‐ Someone, someone's calling me.
I don't know who it is, but
I feel like I can understand
what that person's feeling,
the heartache deep down,
a desire to see someone and talk
to them,
feelings that I have too.
Could this possibly be what
it feels like to be lonely?
‐ [Fakir Voiceover] What
Mytho is regaining his heart.
Look at this face!
I hate this face and its
feelings.
This wretched face
wallowing in its loneliness.
Is it fun recalling such
emotions?
Does it feel good, Mytho?
‐ [Mytho] No.
‐ Right, you have no
need of a heart, Mytho.
None whatsoever.
If you were to regain such
a thing‐‐
‐ If I were?
‐ Don't fall for such
a fool's hope, got that?
‐ Yes.
‐ Speak louder!
‐ Understood, I will do as you
say, Fakir.
‐ [Fakir] Good, as it should be.
‐ [Mr. Cat] Miss Duck,
as punishment for disturbing
the advanced class, you will
practice the develope,
am I understood?
‐ [Duck] Yes, sir.
‐ [Mr. Cat] If you practice
earnestly I'll put you
back with the beginners.
‐ [Duck] Oh, yes sir!
‐ Practice poorly though,
and I'll have you marry me
forthwith!
(Duck screeches in terror)
‐ I'm a bird on probation,
plus I have to stay late.
At this rate I may never
get to be like Rue!
Oh, it's Mytho!
(sighing)
‐ Princess Tutu?
‐ That's just a story!
She's still a princess fated
never to be with her prince.
When she confesses her
love, she turns into a speck
of light and vanishes.
‐ That's just what happens
to Tutu in the story.
The story isn't reality.
Though it is true that
Mytho is a prince from
inside a story.
Oh, who cares?
It doesn't matter if the
story is real or not.
All I wanna do is find the
pieces of Mytho's heart
and give them back to him.
That's right, I'm not
thinking about being with him
or confessing to him
or anything.
I'm not thinking about
any of that!
(soft classical music)
Oh!
‐ [Mytho] I don't really
understand.
‐ It's okay, you can be a dummy,
Mytho.
Now and forever.
Trust me, Mytho, you do love me.
‐ Oh, okay, then I do love you.
‐ Yes, yes, remember that.
You don't need to understand,
and you don't need a heart
either.
What?
‐ This feeling of wanting
to see someone and talk to them,
it stays even when I'm with you.
Could this possibly be
the feeling of loneliness?
I don't know, these emotions
I'm feeling‐‐
‐ Rue!
Would you please stop making
him recall stupid things?
Mytho, go back to your room.
‐ [Mytho] Okay.
‐ You'd better not be the
person who's helping him
dredge up these weird things.
‐ Oh please!
‐ Who else are you saying
could have done it?
‐ Maybe it was Princess Tutu
from the fairy tale.
Maybe she appeared in real life.
‐ Quiet!
Try to stay away from Mytho
from now on.
‐ Stop trying to order me
around!
‐ [Blonde Girl] Huh, Piano?
‐ Where's Duck?
‐ Ah!
‐ [Both] Is that Duck?
‐ Oh, why are you two here?
‐ Hey hey, that's our line.
‐ That's right, we came
here thinking you would be
really depressed because
you had to stay behind.
‐ Why are you so chipper?
‐ Thank you both,
but I'm really having
a lot of fun right now,
because the more you practice
dancing the more fun it becomes!
‐ Oh Duck!
(Duck screams)
Don't force it,
you can exhale when you're sad
or like you're in pain
when you're suffering.
Oh, you were suffering then!
‐ Well it was your fault!
‐ No.
‐ Are you okay?
‐ Yeah, I'm okay.
‐ Say, why don't
we keep her company?
‐ Yeah, good idea!
‐ What? Thank you!
‐ It's fine, after all,
this is for you!
Okay, let's all drop the
probationary class with Duck.
(soft classical music)
You still have a long way to go,
Duck.
‐ [Mr. Cat] Miss Duck!
(girls gasp)
‐ Mr. Cat!
‐ I have some unfortunate news.
(growls)
‐ Uh, unfortunate news?
‐ Yes, Miss Duck, you
have worked much too hard.
Therefore unfortunately, I must
put off having you marry me!
‐ Uh, oh, I see then!
‐ And, I will let you return
to the beginner class.
‐ What? Oh!
Oh thank you so much!
‐ You did it,
I'm so happy for you!
Good job, all right Duck!
(wind whistling)
‐ The wind's picking up.
Oh, Mytho!
‐ [Mytho] What is it
you want me to do?
‐ Who are you talking to?
(Duck gasps)
What, what was?
Uh, Mytho?
Huh, where?
Mytho!
He's gone!
Mytho ahh!
‐ What are you doing?
‐ I'm sorry.
Huh, he's not there!
‐ Were you just calling
for Mytho?
‐ Uh, yeah.
‐ You need something?
‐ No, not need but, I just
saw him come out this way.
‐ What?
There was no one coming out.
‐ Bu, but I'm sure I saw Mytho!
‐ No way, I didn't see anyone
out here.
‐ So, that way then?
‐ It was you!
‐ [Duck] Huh, what?
‐ You cried out rudely when I
was dancing
and interrupted me!
‐ [Duck] Oh, well that was‐‐
‐ You don't seem to have
the slightest comprehension
as to how much focus is
required when dancing!
‐ Oh, if it's about that, sorry!
But more importantly, Mytho
was acting weird just now.
Or rather, acting strange.
That's the same, but anyway,
I gotta find him now.
See ya!
‐ Hold on, we aren't done
talking yet!
Wait just a minute!
(Nutcracker theme)
‐ Mytho, you need to stay away
from Rue!
Mytho?
‐ [Duck Voiceover] It's
strange, definitely strange.
After talking to someone
invisible it's like
time skipped forward and Mytho,
I wonder which way he went?
Uh, Rue?
‐ Your, your name,
it's Duck right?
You run pretty, pretty fast!
‐ Oh, yeah, I know!
‐ Don't mock me!
I'm just a little out of breath,
okay?
So just cut it out!
‐ Okay, sor‐‐
(groans)
Um‐‐
‐ What is it?
‐ Since there are two of us
here,
I was thinking maybe
it would be faster
if we split up and searched
separately.
‐ That, that's true,
you're quite right.
It's rather odd that
someone like you and I
should be walking shoulder
to shoulder to begin with.
‐ Odd?
Yeah, she's right.
Oh, well I'll go look over here.
We can decide on a time or
something and meet up somewhere.
‐ I changed my mind.
‐ What?
Why is that?
‐ It's much more reliable with
two pairs of eyes looking.
‐ Hmm, ya think?
(quirky music)
Um‐‐
‐ [Rue] What is it now?
‐ [Duck] Have you been friends
with Mytho
for a long time now?
‐ [Rue] You keep calling him
Mytho,
that's awfully forward of you!
‐ But Mytho told me that
I could.
‐ And another thing,
we're not exactly friends,
so I'd appreciate it if
you didn't call me Rue.
‐ Then what am I supposed to
call you?
‐ Lady Rue.
‐ Hmm, Lady...
Rue?
‐ What, what's so hard about
that?
‐ [Duck] It's just
weird, I'll call you Rue,
it's cuter that way.
‐ Cuter?
‐ Besides, we've walked together
and talked all this time,
so we're already friends now.
Thus, it's Rue.
Still no Mytho, huh Rue?
‐ [Rue] Hmmph!
‐ Oh!
What's that?
(ghostly sobbing)
They're all, all crying!
‐ It's a funeral, so naturally!
‐ [Both] Mytho!
‐ (panting) Huh?
‐ What?
‐ What's this?
(thunder booming)
A dead end?
(bright music)
What can this be now?
‐ [Duck] Miss Edel!
‐ Good evening Duck, good
evening Rue.
‐ How is it that you know my‐‐
‐ Oh, she knows everything,
even the fact that I'm a bir‐‐
Oh.
‐ Say what?
‐ Anyway, she's nobody
suspicious.
‐ She is too!
‐ Miss Edel,
we were looking for Mytho,
and we saw him here,
but something really weird
happened just now.
He walked into that dead end
with a funeral procession
and vanished!
‐ A story in a story.
‐ Huh, a story?
‐ There once was a beautiful
maiden with a beautiful heart,
and maidens fall in love.
‐ Your story has nothing
to do with finding Mytho!
‐ [Miss Edel] But unlike her
beloved,
this maiden was not noble born.
It was a love never to be
requited.
‐ I just said‐‐
‐ Wait, Rue!
So what happened to the maiden,
Miss Edel?
‐ Devastated,
she took her own life.
‐ Oh!
‐ If her love wouldn't be
requited in this world,
she'd be reborn and see it
fulfilled then.
However, her fiancé never came,
and the maiden took another man
to the world of the dead
in his stead.
This is the maiden's melancholy
story within the story.
Here in this town,
there was a maiden
who met the exact same fate.
As in the story,
she fell in love.
And just as in the story,
she lost hope.
And just as in the story, she
took her own life, and then‐‐
‐ Is the story going to become
real?
‐ [Miss Edel] The story will
become real in this town,
where reality and stories
intermingle.
(bells tolling)
(somber music)
‐ Just as in the story,
Mytho will be taken
in that man's stead.
‐ I won't let that happen!
‐ [Miss Edel] It's starting.
‐ [Girls] Huh?
‐ [Duck] The dead end!
‐ [Rue] A mansion?
‐ [Miss Edel] The maiden's
soul has settled in
that mansion's courtyard.
She has been waiting.
‐ Let's go, Rue!
‐ Yes!
‐ [Duck] Mytho!
‐ I'm that man?
If you say it is true,
then perhaps I am.
‐ Mytho, who are you talking to?
(female giggling)
What's going on?
(soft music)
(rock crunching)
(chimes ringing)
‐ Is she the maiden then?
(chime ringing)
The pendant!
(suspenseful classical music)
‐ So it was you that was
calling to me all of this time.
‐ The rosemary from Giselle?
You mustn't take it!
‐ [Duck] No, Rue!
‐ You'll be taken away
to the world of the dead!
Come over here!
‐ Oh, Rue!
(gasping in effort)
‐ [Rue Voiceover] I don't
have the stamina to dance
Giselle to the end, if only I
had done more basic training.
(gasps in defeat)
‐ Rue!
(female giggling)
‐ No, don't!
‐ Oh no!
‐ Well well, at this rate
the prince will be entering
an eternal slumber.
Is that okay, Princess Tutu?
(laughter)
(chimes ringing)
‐ [Duck] My prince, stop,
you mustn't take it!
‐ Why, why do you interfere?
Who are you?
‐ I am Princess Tutu.
Just like you,
I am fated never to be
with the one whom I love.
Please, come and dance with me.
(lively classical music)
‐ Amazing, she's still
keeping up with her!
‐ If you share
the same fate as I,
then why is your dancing
not laden with sorrow?
‐ Because of the many
other emotions in my heart
that won't give in
to the sorrow.
Even if you take Mytho,
it won't dispel the sorrow,
will it?
Because the sorrow that resides
within you
is not how you truly feel.
I cannot know how much, nor
how long you have suffered.
But I know
whatever your story is,
you have grieved enough
in your heart,
and so you can sleep
in peace now.
Yes, you needn't grieve anymore.
(sighing)
(soft classical music)
This is the shard
of your heart called sorrow,
and it makes people suffer.
But it still is an
important emotion to have.
(chime ringing)
‐ Princess Tutu!
‐ The emotions returning
to the prince
are loneliness and sorrow,
feelings people have
no desire for.
My dear princess,
do you think this will
bring your prince happiness?
(laughs)
(soft music)
(soft singing in Japanese)
‐ [Duck] Mytho, he's a prince,
is this the real you, Mytho?
‐ [Mytho] Will you be going
today, Duck?
‐ [Rue] I was a fool for
believing what Duck said.
‐ [Fakir] When you were
wandering,
completely stripped
of your memories,
I was the one who gave
you the name of Mytho.
‐ [Ghost] My only wish is
to keep on
shining for someone.
Somewhere along the way I
had simply become forgotten.
‐ [Duck] It's sad that
they no longer need you,
but it's something
that can't be helped.
‐ [Drosselmeyer] All who
love stories gather round.
(laughter)