-ONCE UPON A TIME,
THERE WAS A GIRL WHO LOVED
FLOWERS MORE THAN ANYONE.
SHE PRAYED EVERY DAY
FOR THE WHOLE TOWN TO BE FILLED
WITH BEAUTIFUL FLOWERS.
TO MAKE THAT HAPPEN,
SHE PULLED UP
ALL THE TOWN'S UGLY WEEDS.
EVENTUALLY, THE GIRL'S PRAYERS
WERE ANSWERED,
AND THE TOWN
WAS BLANKETED IN FLOWERS.
BUT THEY SAY THE TOWN
THAT WAS FILLED
WITH INNUMERABLE BLOSSOMS
OF EVERY COLOR IMAGINABLE
SOMEHOW LOOKED GRAY.
[ RITSUKO OKAZAKI'S
"MORNING GRACE" PLAYS ]
-[ SINGING IN JAPANESE ]
[ SINGING CONTINUES ]
[ THUNDER RUMBLING ]
[ KNOCK ON DOOR ]
-RUE?
ARE YOU THERE?
RUE.
RUE CAME BACK LOOKING
LIKE HER USUAL SELF AGAIN,
NOT AT ALL LIKE KRAEHE.
BUT THERE'S SOMETHING DIFFERENT.
COULD SHE REALLY BE KRAEHE
AFTER ALL?
IS IT KRAEHE'S FAULT
THAT MYTHO TRIED TO TAKE
PIKE'S HEART FROM HER?
IS SOMETHING HAPPENING BEHIND
THE SCENES WHERE I CAN'T SEE IT?
[ THUNDER CRASHES ]
I DON'T WANT TO FIGHT ANYMORE.
-SAY, WHY DON'T YOU
FIGHT ONE MORE TIME?
-NO!
-BUT CHANCES LIKE THIS ARE RARE.
A MAGNIFICENT BATTLE WOULD BE --
-FORGET IT!
-DARN.
-I MEAN, YOU KNOW, SURE,
I WAS INTO MYTHO FOR A TIME,
BUT FRANKLY MY PASSION
HAS COOLED.
AT THIS POINT, I REALLY
DON'T CARE ALL THAT MUCH.
IN THE END,
I'VE ALWAYS BEEN A FAKIR GIRL.
-YEAH, HE'S DEFINITELY BEEN COOL
LATELY, HASN'T HE?
-LIKE THAT AIR OF MYSTERY
HE HAS.
-THE AIR OF HIS SHADY CROOK.
-AND THAT SLIGHTLY DARK AURA.
-OH, YEAH, THE GLOOMY MOOD.
-WANT TO BATTLE?
-BRING IT ON.
-EH...NO!
-AAH!
-COME ON, GUYS!
A BATTLE?
-HAVE YOU BECOME A FAKIR GIRL,
TOO?
-OOH!
-A THREE-WAY FIGHT!
-N-N-N-N-NO WAY!
I'M SAYING
I DON'T LIKE FIGHTING.
I MEAN, YOU TWO SHOULDN'T FIGHT.
-HUH?
-IT'S SENIOR MYTHO AND MR. RUE.
-WOW, HOW FINE.
-OHH.
-HE'S SO DIVINE.
-WHY WOULD SHE HURT HERSELF?
-IS MS. RUE HURT?
-HE'S SO WONDERFUL.
-HER GETTING HURT
MIGHT NOT BE SO BAD.
-UH...
H-HEY, UH -- OH.
-I HAVE DIVINE NEWS
FOR ALL YOU LADIES.
THE GOLD CROWN ACADEMY
FINE ARTS WEEK STARTS TOMORROW,
AND MR. MYTHO SAYS
THAT WHOEVER WINS
THIS BALLET CONTEST, HE WILL
MAKE HER HIS PARTNER
IN THE EXHIBITION
IN PLACE OF MS. RUE,
WHO IS INJURED
AND UNABLE TO DANCE.
[ EXCLAIMS OF JOY ]
DON'T REJOICE YET, LADIES.
I HAVEN'T FINISHED.
-HUH?
-THE RUNNER-UP WILL HAVE THE
INCREDIBLY DESIRABLE OPPORTUNITY
TO BE MY PARTNER.
WHAT'S MORE -- MY LIFE PARTNER!
YES, A MARRIAGE,
MARRIAGE, VIVA MARR--
[ WIND HOWLING ]
OH. I UNDERSTAND.
THIS MUST MEAN EVERYONE
IS AIMING FOR RUNNER-UP
AND HAS BEGUN
PRACTICING HARD RIGHT AWAY!
ME-O-O-OW!
MEOW-MEOW, MEOW-MEOW-WOW-WOW!
MEOW, MEOW, MEOW.
-MYTHO AND RUE --
I THOUGHT I SAW HIM GO THIS WAY.
-IT'S NOT SO EASY
PRETENDING TO BE INJURED.
-PRETENDING?
THEN SHE LIED?
-SO DO IT RIGHT THIS TIME.
-I KNOW, KRAEHE.
-KRAEHE?
HE CALLED HER KRAEHE.
MYTHO.
[ GASPS ]
[ SIGHS ]
-BLOOM PRETTILY.
YOU, TOO.
AND YOU, TOO.
-WOW.
-UH.
-OH, I'M REALLY SORRY.
I DIDN'T MEAN TO INTRUDE.
-IT'S FINE.
THIS GARDEN
BELONGS TO EVERYBODY.
-SO PRETTY.
-AREN'T THEY?
-HUH?
I DIDN'T MEAN THAT!
OH!
I MEAN, OF COURSE
THE FLOWERS ARE PRETTY!
BUT, YOU KNOW, THAT'S
NOT ALL MISS, UH -- MISS, UH...
-MY NAME'S FREYA.
-OH.
MY NAME IS DUCK.
THIS IS AMAZING.
DID YOU GROW ALL THESE FLOWERS,
MS. FREYA?
-FLOWERS BLOOM ON THEIR OWN.
I SIMPLY PRAY.
BLOOM PRETTILY.
BLOOM ABUNDANTLY.
-SAY, WHY AREN'T YOU PRACTICING
RIGHT NOW LIKE EVERYONE ELSE?
-FOR THE ART FESTIVAL
COMPETITION?
-YEAH.
-I LIKE BALLET JUST LIKE YOU DO,
SO I WILL PRACTICE LATER.
FIRST, I MUST CARE
FOR THESE LITTLE ONES.
-WOW, YOU REALLY LOVE FLOWERS,
DON'T YOU?
-YES.
WELL, IT WOULD BE WONDERFUL
IF THE WORLD WERE FULL
OF FLOWERS, WOULDN'T IT?
-MS. FREYA IS WHAT'S WONDERFUL.
IT MAKES ME WISH
I COULD BECOME THIS WONDERFUL.
BUT I --
-YOU DON'T HAVE IT, ZURA.
-WHAT, REALLY?
-REALLY, ZURA.
-NOT AT ALL?
-NOT AT ALL, ZURA.
WAIT, WHO'S THERE?
-IT'S NOT HERE, ZURA!
WHERE DID YOU HIDE IT, ZURA?
-HUH?
WHAT'S NOT?
-YOUR DUCK'S TAIL, ZURA.
-WHAT?
WHAT DO YOU MEAN "DUCK"?
-WHERE IS IT, ZURA?
-QUACK! OHH.
-OH.
-QUACK. Q-Q--
-AH! YOU'RE A DUCK, ZURA.
OH! THERE'S YOUR TAIL, ZURA.
-QUACK!
QUACK! QUACK!
[ DRUM BEATING ]
[ CLASSICAL MUSIC PLAYING ]
OHH.
JUST WHO WAS THAT KID ANYWAY?
THANKS TO HER, I WAS LATE,
AND NOW I HAVE DETENTION.
-YOUR --
-HUH?
THAT VOICE IS --
-I'M NOT REALLY HOPING TO WIN.
-IT'S HER.
IT IS MS. FREYA.
-DO YOU HATE ME?
-UH -- AND MYTHO?
-OF COURSE NOT.
-YOUR BEAUTIFUL HEART
MAKES BEAUTIFUL FLOWERS BLOOM.
IF WE PUT OUR ABILITIES
TOGETHER,
I'M SURE WE COULD MAKE
A NEW KIND OF FLOWER BLOOM
THAT NO ONE'S EVER SEEN.
NOBODY ELSE HAS A HEART
SO BEAUTIFUL AS TO HAVE
THE DESIRE TO MAKE THE WORLD
HAPPY WITH DANCING AND FLOWERS.
SURELY, EVEN YOU BELIEVE THAT,
DON'T YOU?
-I CAN'T SAY I EVER --
-IT'S ALL RIGHT TO THINK THAT...
BECAUSE YOU'RE DIFFERENT
FROM ALL THOSE NOBODIES.
AND YOU'LL WIN THE COMPETITION.
THAT'S RIGHT.
EVERYONE AROUND YOU
IS YOUR ENEMY.
LOVE ONLY ME
AND HATE EVERYONE ELSE.
-YES.
-PROMISE TO LOVE ONLY ME.
-ALL RIGHT.
-PROMISE ME
THAT YOU'LL HATE EVERYONE ELSE.
-I WILL.
I PROMISE TO LOVE ONLY YOU
AND TO HATE EVERYONE ELSE, TOO.
-NOT AGAIN!
-THESE BLOOMS -- THE ROOM
IS FULL OF FLOWERS WE'VE NEVER
SEEN BEFORE, ISN'T IT IT, MYTHO?
-TUTU.
-MS. FREYA.
WILL YOU HATE EVERYONE?
BUT THE REAL YOU DOESN'T WANT
TO HATE EVEN ONE PERSON,
DOES SHE?
-NO, BUT MYTHO SAYS
THAT HE DESIRES IT, SO --
-TUTU.
HELP...ME.
-MYTHO.
-MYTHO?
-MYTHO!
MS. FREYA!
-THE RAVEN'S BLOOD
STILL HASN'T SOAKED YOU THROUGH?
HURRY UP AND BECOME MY PRINCE
AND MINE ALONE,
THE PRINCE
WHO LOVES ME AND ME ALONE.
-THE STORY IS PROGRESSING
DEEPLY, QUIETLY IN A PLACE
WHERE LITTLE DUCK CAN'T SEE IT.
[ LAUGHS EVILLY ]
WE WILL BE OPENING THE BALLET
COMPETITION MOMENTARILY.
AS ANNOUNCED PREVIOUSLY,
THE WINNER WILL DANCE
WITH MR. MYTHO AS HIS PARTNER.
-OH, I'M SO JEALOUS!
-THE RUNNER-UP, OF COURSE,
WILL HAVE THE PRIVILEGE
AND PLEASURE OF DANCING
ETERNALLY AS MY PARTNER!
-[ CRYING ]
-THE PARTICIPANTS MUST BE
FEELING A NERVOUSNESS SUCH
AS THEY'VE NEVER FELT BEFORE.
-THAT'S FOR SURE.
-WELL, IF THEY WIN, IT'S HEAVEN.
BUT IF THEY MAKE ONE FALSE STEP,
IT'S HELL.
-WITH THAT, LET US NOW
BEGIN THE COMPETITION.
EVERYBODY TRY YOUR BEST
AIMING FOR THIS MUCH-COVETED
RUNNER-UP BOUQUET!
[ CLASSICAL MUSIC PLAYING ]
-THE WONDERFUL MYTHO
IS WATCHING.
I DON'T WANT TO LOSE...
-...NO MATTER WHAT.
-THE ONE
TO BECOME HIS PARTNER...
-...WILL BE ME.
-THE TENSION'S SUFFOCATING.
-OH, I WISH DUCK COULD HAVE BEEN
IN THE CONTEST, TOO.
-ACTUALLY, WHERE IS DUCK?
-WHAT?
DOES SHE NOT CARE AT ALL
WHO BECOMES THE WONDERFUL
MYTHO'S PARTNER?
-DOES THAT MEAN SHE'S COMPLETELY
BECOME A FAKIR GIRL NOW?
-AAH!
I SENSE A BATTLE.
-COME ON.
-MYTHO PROBABLY
CAN'T DO ANYTHING FUNNY
DURING THE CONTEST.
I'M KIND OF JUST SHOWING UP.
I HOPE FAKIR WILL BE HOME.
[ DRUM BEATING ]
QUA--
HER AGAIN?
-HEY.
WHAT ARE YOU DOING HERE?
-OH, FAKIR.
-FAKIR!
-HUH?
I-I-I C-C-CAME TO SEE YOU,
FAKIR, B-BUT THIS GIRL --
-SHE HAD A BUTT, ZURA!
-DID YOU DO SOMETHING TO HER?
-I WAS LOOKING FOR HER TAIL,
AND I FOUND HER BUTT, ZURA!
-NOW, LOOK, YOU.
-QUACK!
-OH!
-QUACK.
HER NECK.
HER NECK. HER NECK.
-HEY.
-HER NECK JUST TWISTED.
HE TWISTED HER NECK.
HE TWISTED IT AROUND.
-WHY ARE YOU HIDING, ZURA?
-SHUT UP!
HERE. ALL RIGHT, NOW.
HAVE YOU AT LEAST
CALMED DOWN A LITTLE BIT?
-YES. THANK YOU.
WHO IS SHE?
-WELL, HER NAME IS UZURA.
KARON, HE MADE HER FROM THE WOOD
FROM EDEL THAT DIDN'T BURN UP.
-FROM MS. EDEL.
OH, SO, IS THAT WHY
SHE KNEW ME ALREADY?
-WHAT?
NO, I TOLD HER ABOUT YOU.
-HUH?
-I TOLD HER ABOUT YOU AND MYTHO
AND THINGS.
BUT IT LOOKS
LIKE EDEL'S MEMORIES ARE GONE.
SHE WARMED MY BODY
AND BECAME A GUIDING FLAME
FOR YOU AND MYTHO.
-MS. EDEL.
SHE REALLY DID SAVE OUR LIVES
THAT NIGHT.
EVEN LIKE THIS,
I'M GLAD I GET TO SEE HER AGAIN.
NOW THAT YOU SAY IT,
SHE KIND OF DOES REMIND ME OF --
OH! QUACK!
QUA-QUACK!
-HUH? OH!
-WHATCHA DOING, ZURA?
-JUST SHUT UP.
ANYWAY, DUCK, DIDN'T YOU HAVE
SOME REASON FOR COMING?
-YES.
IT HAS TO DO WITH MYTHO.
A FEW DAYS AGO, HE
TRIED TO TAKE PIKE'S HEART OUT.
IT DIDN'T WORK, THOUGH, SO NOW
HE'S TRYING TO DO THE SAME THING
TO MS. FREYA.
-THE HEART SHARD OF LOVE THAT
PRINCESS TUTU GAVE BACK TO HIM,
THAT SHARD WAS SOAKED IN A BATH
OF THE RAVEN'S BLOOD,
SO HE'LL LOVE ONLY ME.
AND HE'LL FIND A YOUNG
AND BEAUTIFUL HEART
FOR MY FATHER AND GIVE IT TO HIM
AS A SACRIFICE.
-DID YOU TELL TUTU
ABOUT ALL THIS?
-I SHOULD.
IF I DID THAT, I COULD MAKE
HER SUFFER, COULDN'T I?
-SO, UH, WHAT DO YOU THINK
HAPPENED TO MYTHO?
FIND OUT ANYTHING?
-MM...
NO.
NOTHING.
-WELL, ALL RIGHT.
THAT'S ALL.
I JUST THOUGHT YOU MIGHT HAVE
FOUND OUT SOMETHING,
SO I CAME TO SEE IF YOU HAD.
-RIGHT.
-I'M WORRIED ABOUT MS. FREYA,
SO I'M GONNA GO BACK.
-WAIT.
-HUH?
-I THINK I'LL GO WITH YOU.
UZURA,
I'M LEAVING YOU TO HOUSE-SIT.
-LEAVE IT TO ME, ZURA!
-LET'S GO.
-GREAT.
-EDEL?
I DON'T GET IT, ZURA!
[ CLASSICAL MUSIC CONTINUES ]
-THIS IS NO GOOD.
-THE DANCING'S FINE, BUT
THEIR EXPRESSIONS DON'T WORK.
-AS IT STANDS, THERE'S NO ONE
WHO QUALIFIES FOR WINNER
OR RUNNER-UP.
-UH, NEXT CONTESTANT.
HMM?
[ GASPS ]
-WHAT NOVEL DANCING.
-ABOVE ALL,
SHE HAS GREAT EXPRESSIONS.
-PUT HER ON THE SHORT LIST.
-AAH! NEXT PLEASE!
-WOW.
-IT LOOKS LIKE A VICTORY...
-...HAS BEEN DECIDED.
-OH, NO.
YOU MEAN THE RUNNER-UP?
PLEASE MAKE HER THE RUNNER-UP.
-VERY SOON NOW, FATHER.
-WHAT A LOVELY FRAGRANCE.
I CAN SMELL THE SWEET SCENT
FROM HERE.
I CAN HARDLY STAND IT.
-THIS TIME, I WILL MOST
CERTAINLY BRING TO YOU A HEART
THAT SHINES BLACKLY, FATHER.
-AND THAT WILL BE THE TIME
WHEN YOUR EFFORTS SHALL REAP
THE REWARD, MY DAUGHTER.
-YES, DEAR FATHER.
-LEAVE MYTHO TO ME.
YOU NEED TO SAVE FREYA.
-BUT IF WE JUST TALK TO MYTHO --
-YOU NEED TO DO AS I TELL YOU.
-UH...ALL RIGHT.
-FLAWLESS.
SHE'S THE WINNER.
-YES!
-CONGRATULATIONS, FREYA.
MY LOVE BELONGS TO YOU.
-SO, SHE REALLY DID WIN.
WHICH MEANS THE RUNNER-UP --
AAH!
-OKAY.
-UNFORTUNATELY, THIS YEAR,
NO ONE QUALIFIED FOR RUNNER-UP,
AND, WITH THAT,
I DECLARE THE COMPETITION OVER.
-IT'S OVER.
-OH, THAT'S RIGHT!
-HEY!
-LOVE ONLY ME, FREYA.
I WANT YOU TO HATE
EVERYBODY ELSE.
YOUR HEART IS YOUNG
AND BEAUTIFUL.
DYED BLACK,
IT GIVES OFF A STRONG FRAGRANCE.
YOU'LL GIVE IT TO ME, WON'T YOU?
-I WILL.
-DANCE, FREYA.
DANCE AS PROOF
OF YOUR LOVE FOR ME
AND GIVE ME YOUR HEART.
-GIVE ME YOUR HEART.
-MS. FREYA.
-FAKIR!
WAIT.
PLEASE, COME DANCE WITH ME,
MS. FREYA.
-TU--
HMM.
QUIT SHOWING YOUR FACE.
HURRY AND VANISH.
-AGAIN YOU WOULD TRY TO COME
BETWEEN MYTHO AND ME?
I WON'T HAVE IT!
-MS. FREYA!
-YES, THAT'S IT,
MY LITTLE FLOWER.
COME INTO MY ARMS, FREYA.
-PULL YOURSELF TOGETHER, MYTHO!
-MS. FREYA, IS THAT LOVE REAL?
WEREN'T FLOWERS YOUR HOPE,
YOUR PRAYER, YOUR WISH?
-YOU'RE RIGHT.
THAT IS WHAT I DESIRE,
WHAT I PRAY FOR.
NOW LOOK AROUND.
SEE HOW MANY HAVE BLOOMED?
-IS THIS REALLY WHAT YOU
WANTED THEM TO LOOK LIKE?
LISTEN CLOSELY TO THE VOICES
OF THE FLOWERS YOU LOVE.
-THE FLOWERS' VOICES?
I CAN'T.
I CAN'T HEAR THEM.
-WATCH.
WATCH TUTU'S DANCE.
-I CAN'T HEAR THEM.
I CAN'T HEAR
THE FLOWERS' VOICES.
-DON'T GIVE UP.
REMEMBER.
REMEMBER YOUR PRAYER.
-MY PRAYER.
-YES, YOUR PRAYER
FOR EVERYBODY TO BE HAPPY.
THAT WAS WHAT YOU WISHED FOR,
WASN'T IT, MS. FREYA?
-OH, I HEAR THEM,
THE FLOWERS' VOICES.
-MYTHO, REMEMBER!
-WHY WON'T YOU LOVE ME?
WHY?
-MYTHO, REMEMBER YOUR REAL SELF!
-MY REAL...SELF.
-DON'T LET YOUR EARS
BE POISONED BY SOME KNIGHT
TOO SELFISH TO DIE.
-KRAEHE.
-THE WAY YOU ARE NOW
IS THE REAL MYTHO.
-KRAEHE,
WHAT HAVE YOU DONE TO MYTHO?
-THE ONE WHO MADE THE PRINCE
LIKE THIS IS YOU, TUTU.
-STOP IT.
-AFTER ALL,
YOU RETURNED THE FEELING OF LOVE
TO THE PRINCE
IGNORANT OF THE FACT THAT IT WAS
DYED IN THE RAVEN'S BLOOD.
YOU DIDN'T TELL HER, FAKIR?
I'M FOREVER IN YOUR DEBT, TUTU.
-MYTHO.
-HEY.
ARE YOU ANGRY WITH ME
BECAUSE I KEPT IT FROM YOU?
-A LITTLE.
-I'M SORRY, DUCK.
-MYTHO IS MYTHO, RIGHT?
EVEN WITH RAVEN'S BLOOD IN HIM,
MYTHO IS MYTHO.
HE'LL GO BACK TO HIS OLD SELF,
RIGHT?
-OF COURSE.
-UZURA'S WAITING FOR US.
-YOU BE CAREFUL OF UZURA.
-HUH?
-CONGRATULATIONS, LITTLE DUCK.
NOW THERE'S ONE LESS THING
YOU DON'T KNOW.
BUT PERHAPS IGNORANCE
WAS BETTER.
[ LAUGHS EVILLY ]
-[ SINGING IN JAPANESE ]
[ SINGING IN JAPANESE
CONTINUES ]
-I AM QUALIFIED
TO BE A TRUE PRINCE,
ONE WHO LOVES EVERYONE
AND IS ALSO LOVED BY EVERYONE.
-I ALREADY TOLD YOU
THERE IS NO RUE.
-THAT'S NOT TRUE!
I DON'T BELIEVE THAT.
I GET THIS FEELING
YOU'RE STILL RUE.
-PROMISE TO LOVE ONLY ME.
HATE EVERYONE ELSE.
-WHEN PEOPLE SAY DUCK GOES WELL
TOGETHER AND IS LOVEY-DOVEY,
WHAT'S IT MEAN, ZURA?
-WHAT?
DUCK IS?
WITH WHOM?
-A FEELING EXPRESSED
WITHOUT EVEN A WORD.
-THAT'S THE MIME
FOR "I LOVE YOU."
-ALL YOU CHILDREN WHO LOVE
STORIES, COME GATHER 'ROUND.