-ONCE UPON A TIME...
THERE WAS A GIRL WHO LOVED
TO DANCE VERY MUCH.
THE GIRL MADE THE MISTAKE
OF PUTTING ON A PAIR
OF RED SHOES THAT, ONCE PUT ON,
WOULD FORCE HER TO DANCE
FOR ETERNITY.
THE GIRL CONTINUED TO DANCE
DAY AND NIGHT.
OOPS.
THIS IS A DIFFERENT STORY.
ALTHOUGH, PERHAPS IT IS NOT
SO COMPLETELY DIFFERENT
AFTER ALL.
[ RITSUKO OKAZAKI'S
"MORNING GRACE" PLAYING ]
-♪ YONDE IRU KOE ♪
♪ SAA ME O SAMASHITE ♪
♪ NAKIGAO NUGUTTE ♪
♪ MABUSHII HIKARI ♪
♪ KIGI NO TSUYU ♪
♪ UMARERU ♪
♪ DARE MO SHIRANAI ♪
♪ HIMITSU NO MIZUBE DE ♪
♪ ODORE INOCHI NO PA DO DU ♪
♪ KYOU MO YUME MITERU ♪
♪ SORE WA YASASHIKU ♪
♪ HAGESHII NAGARE NE ♪
♪ DOKO MADE TSUZUKU RABIRINSU ♪
♪ WATASHI WA YUKOU ♪
♪ NIGIRISHIMERU YUME ♪
[ TCHAIKOVSKY'S
"WALTZ OF THE FLOWERS" PLAYING ]
-[ GASPS ]
-WHAT DO YOU THINK OF ME?
I WANT TO KNOW.
-I...UH, I...
[ Thinking ] I'M A DUCK.
I'M REALLY ONLY A BIRD.
BUT WHAT THE PRINCE SEES
IS PRINCESS TUTU
IN HER BEAUTIFUL DRESS.
IT'S NOT ME.
[ WATER FLOWING ]
-WHAT DID I DO JUST NOW?
[ RAVENS CAWING ]
[ BIRDS CHIRPING ]
-[ GROANS ]
[ Thinking ] SOME THINGS
JUST DON'T CHANGE
AFTER A NIGHT'S SLEEP.
RUE AND MYTHO ARE STILL
PERFECT FOR EACH OTHER.
FAKIR IS STILL NOT NICE.
I'M STILL A DUCK.
AND OUTSIDE THE WINDOW,
THE SKY IS AS WIDE OPEN
AS EVER.
THERE'S NO PROBLEM!
[ BELLS RINGING ]
-[ Thinking ] I AM RUE.
I'M NOT ANYONE ELSE.
THAT'S WHO I'VE ALWAYS BEEN.
AND WHO I ALWAYS WILL BE.
[ GASPS ]
[ CAWS ]
-RUE.
-YES, WHAT?
I WANT TO KNOW.
I WANT TO KNOW WHETHER
I LOVE YOU OR NOT, RUE.
-I WANT TO HEAR YOU SAY
THAT YOU LOVE ME.
-YES, RUE, I LOVE YOU.
-TRUST ME, MYTHO,
YOU DO LOVE ME.
-OKAY. THEN I DO LOVE YOU.
DO I REALLY LOVE YOU?
-YOU DO.
-THEN WHAT IS THIS THAT I FEEL
WHEN I'M THINKING OF TUTU?
-[ SCOFFS ]
TUTU.
-RUE, MAYBE I'M ACTUALLY...
-DON'T BOTHER ME
WITH THAT NONSENSE!
[ INDISTINCT CONVERSATIONS ]
-WHAT'S GONNA HAPPEN!
-RUINED? WILL THEY BE RUINED?
OH, THEY'LL BE RUINED,
WON'T THEY?
-WITH THIS HAND,
I TRIED TO PIERCE MYTHO'S HEART.
ON THE GROUNDS THAT DOING SO
WOULD BE
IN MYTHO'S BEST INTERESTS.
BUT SINCE MYTHO HIMSELF WISHES
TO REGAIN HIS HEART,
WHAT CAN I DO NOW THAT
NOTHING I DO CAN DETER HIM?
IS THERE ANYTHING AT ALL
THAT REMAINS FOR ME?
OTHER THAN ACCEPTING FATE
BY HIS SIDE WITHOUT TREMBLING?
[ GASPS ] TREMBLING.
AM I THE ONE WHO'S AFRAID?
-HOW 'BOUT THE PIZZERIA?
-WHAT?
-YOU DON'T KNOW IT?
IT'S THE RED BUILDING
ON CHURCH STREET.
-NO, I DON'T.
SO WHAT ABOUT THIS PIZZERIA?
-WHAT DO YOU THINK?
-UH...
-COME ON, WHAT ELSE?
-HUH?
-YOUR REVENGE!
-WHAT?! WHAT REVENGE?
-FOR YOUR CONFESSION, OF COURSE.
-HUH?
-NOW THAT MYTHO AND RUE
HAVE FALLEN INTO RUIN,
THIS IS YOUR CHANCE.
-WHAT DO YOU MEAN?
-WELL, YOUR CONFESSION
THE OTHER DAY
WAS KIND OF LUKEWARM.
-NO!
-NOW YOU CAN CONFESS AGAIN!
-OR RATHER,
GET TURNED DOWN AGAIN.
-THAT'S NOT WHAT IT WAS!
AND WHAT DO YOU MEAN "RUINED"?
HUH? HUH?
-[ SNICKERS ]
-IN OTHER WORDS,
NOW'S YOUR CHANCE!
-CONFESSION! CONFESSION!
-NO, I CAN'T!
-YOU BIG COWARD!
-[ GROANS ]
-YOU SHOULD ROLL DOWN
THE HALLWAY!
-IT'S YOUR FAULT!
-REALLY?
-YOU AGAIN, MISS DUCK?
[ GROANS ]
ROLLING DOWN THE HALLWAY.
IF YOU KEEP THIS UP,
I WILL HAVE NO CHOICE
BUT TO HAVE YOU MARRY ME!
-I-I AM SO SORRY!
SOMETHING'S ROLLING DOWN
THE HALL!
IT'S COMING REALLY FAST!
-[ SCREAMS ]
WHAT?
[ GASPS ]
MS. GOATETTE.
-IF YOU ROLL DOWN THE HALLWAY,
YOU'LL BE FORCED TO MARRY
MR. CAT!
-[ HISSES ]
[ MEOWS ]
[ DOOR OPENS ]
-YOU AGAIN, HUH?
COME TO READ THAT BOOK?
♪
-HEY, WHAT ABOUT INVITING HIM
TO YOUR HOUSE?
-HOUSE?
-OH! WHERE IS YOUR HOUSE, DUCK?
-UH, THE LAKE.
-THE LAKE?
-I MEAN, IT'S OUT
TOWARDS THE LAKE.
-SO I GUESS IT'S OUTSIDE TOWN,
HUH?
-AFTER ALL, THE ONLY THING
IN TOWN IS THAT POND.
-ALL RIGHT, EVERYONE,
THAT WILL BE IT
FOR THE BEGINNER CLASS LESSON.
THE NEXT HOUR --
[ DOOR OPENS ]
-[ MEOWS ]
[ YOWLS ]
THE PRIVATE LESSON
FOR THE ADVANCED CLASS
WILL BE STARTING AFTER THIS,
SO PLEASE VACATE THE ROOM
IMMEDIATELY.
IF YOU DAWDLE OR HANG ABOUT,
I WILL HAVE YOU MARRY ME!
[ INDISTINCT CONVERSATIONS ]
UH, MS. GOATETTE'S
DAWDLING AND HANGING ABOUT.
-IT SEEMS YOU'LL HAVE
TO GET MARRIED.
-[ YOWLING ]
-[ BLEATS ]
-HUH?
-[ ALL GASPING ]
-MYTHO.
-YOUR CHANCE!
-[ GASPS ]
-OH.
♪
-WONDERFUL AS EVER, HUH?
-DOESN'T LOOK LIKE
THERE'S AN OPENING FOR DUCK.
-DON'T LOSE HEART, DUCK.
-THAT'S RIGHT.
AFTER ALL, WE ALREADY KNEW
THIS WAS THE CASE.
-[ Thinking ] I KNOW.
MYTHO IS PERFECT FOR RUE.
[ Thinking ]
I KNOW THAT I'M JUST A DUCK.
-WHAT DO YOU THINK OF ME?
I WANT TO KNOW.
-[ Thinking ] I KNOW EXACTLY
WHAT I THINK OF MYTHO.
BUT I CAN'T SAY IT.
-IF YOU CHOOSE
TO BECOME PRINCESS TUTU,
YOU CAN SAVE YOUR DEAR PRINCE.
BUT IF YOU PROCLAIM
YOUR LOVE TO HIM,
YOU'LL TURN INTO
A SPECK OF LIGHT AND VANISH.
[ LAUGHS EVILLY ]
-[ Thinking ] I KNOW,
BUT SOMEHOW
MY HEART STILL ACHES.
-[ Thinking ] YOU DON'T HAVE TO
CHANGE AT ALL.
YOU'RE FINE JUST AS YOU ARE.
WHY MUST YOU KEEP TRYING
TO CHANGE WHEN I DON'T WANT TO,
WHEN I WANT THINGS
TO STAY AS THEY ARE?
-[ GASPS ]
PRINCESS TUTU.
-WHAT IN THE WORLD IS THERE
THAT I NEED FEAR?
[ PAGES RUSTLE ]
-RIDICULOUS.
"THE PRINCE AND THE CROW."
THE STORY THAT IS WRITTEN HERE
IS MYTHO'S TALE.
THE FATE OF A FOOLISH PRINCE
WHO TRIED TO PROTECT THE WEAK,
BUT ONLY ENDED UP
HURTING HIMSELF
AND LOSING HIS OWN HEART.
THAT'S ALL.
-MAY THOSE WHO ACCEPT
THEIR FATE BE GRANTED HAPPINESS.
MAY THOSE WHO DEFY IT,
BE GRANTED GLORY.
-YOU'RE --
-THE STORY IS CONTINUING.
THE STORY IS ALIVE.
-ARE YOU SAYING
THIS IS MY FATE?
-[ SIGHS ]
IS IT SAD FOR MYTHO, FOR RUE,
FOR DUCK, OR FOR...
[ CLATTERING ]
-YOU KNOW, RUE,
YOU REALLY DANCE BEAUTIFULLY
EN POINTE.
AND WHEN YOU AND MYTHO DANCE,
IT'S ALWAYS SO WONDERFUL.
I'D LOVE TO DANCE LIKE THAT,
BUT THERE'S NO WAY I CAN YET.
-DID YOU WANT SOMETHING?
-OH. UH, WELL...
EARLIER YOU MENTIONED
PRINCESS TUTU.
-JUST WHAT ARE YOU
PRATTLING ON ABOUT?
A FAIRY TALE LIKE THAT
IS OF NO IMPORTANCE.
-YOU'RE YOUR USUAL SELF.
-OF COURSE I AM.
I'M NOT GOING TO CHANGE.
IF YOU WANNA SAY SOMETHING,
HURRY UP.
-THERE'S NOTHING REALLY.
YOU KNOW, I THINK THE FIRST
PERSON TO DANCE EN POINTE
WAS INCREDIBLE! DON'T YOU?
-THERE'S A STORY ABOUT
THE TOE SHOES
OF THE FIRST PERSON
TO DANCE EN POINTE.
DO YOU KNOW WHAT HAPPENED
TO THEM?
-WHAT? UH, NO.
-WELL, THEY WERE EATEN.
-THEY WHAT?!
-BY A PERSON TO WORSHIPPED
THAT BALLERINA.
-THAT'S KIND OF AMAZING.
-IT'S A STUPID STORY.
-HUH?
-STRANGE.
-WHAT?! NO! WHERE? HUH?
WHAT'S STRANGE?
HUH? HUH? HUH? HUH? HUH?
-I'VE NEVER TALKED LIKE THIS
WITH ANOTHER GIRL BEFORE.
-OH.
DO YOU HATE THIS KIND OF THING?
-I DON'T THINK I HATE IT.
-I'M GLAD. SO WE CAN BECOME
EVEN BETTER FRIENDS, RIGHT?
-YOU THINK?
-HEY, HEY, RUE.
TEACH ME ABOUT GOING EN POINTE.
-AND WHY SHOULD I TEACH YOU?
-BECAUSE WE'RE FRIENDS.
-YOU'VE GOT A LOT OF CHEEK.
-HEY, RUE?
-NOW WHAT?
-UM, IS THAT GIRL
YOUR FRIEND, TOO? [ GASPS ]
-WHERE? WHAT GIRL IS THIS?
-SHE DISAPPEARED. [ LAUGHS ]
-[ SIGHS ]
[ TCHAIKOVSKY'S "DANCE OF
THE SUGAR PLUM FAIRY" PLAYING ]
-AND THAT CONCLUDES
TODAY'S LECTURE ON --
-[ BLEATS ]
-[ YOWLS ]
-GOOD-BYE, MISS RUE.
SEE YOU LATER.
-I BID YOU GOOD AFTERNOON.
-DO YOUR BEST IN DETENTION!
-DON'T BE GLUM. YOUR FEATHERS
ARE WHAT MAKE YOU, DUCK.
-SO, DUCK,
YOU CAN'T GO HOME YET?
-HUH?
-YEAH, I HAVE TO STAY AND WIPE
THE WINDOWS AS PUNISHMENT.
-OH.
FRIENDS.
[ RAVENS CAWING ]
-[ EXHALES DEEPLY ]
THAT'S THE GIRL FROM...
[ BIRDS CHIRPING ]
-SHE WENT INTO THE ART BUILDING.
SO SHE STUDIES DRAWING, HUH?
[ RAVENS CAWING ]
-HI, RUE!
-LADY...RUE?
-WHAT? WHAT'S SO HARD
ABOUT THAT?
-BESIDES, WE'VE WALKED TOGETHER
AND TALKED ALL THIS TIME,
SO WE'RE ALREADY FRIENDS NOW.
RUE.
YOU'RE LIKE A REAL PRINCESS
AND YOU REALLY SUIT EACH OTHER,
SO I'M SURE YOU'LL GET
THE GOLDEN APPLE, TOO.
YOU REALLY SUIT EACH OTHER,
SO...
-SUIT EACH OTHER?
-IT'S JUST AN IDEA
YOU'VE GOT STUCK IN YOUR HEAD.
-[ BLEATING ]
-OH, YOU MAY THINK YOU NEED ME
BUT THE SIMPLE FACT REMAINS,
I DO NOT NEED YOU.
-[ BLEATS ]
-[ Thinking ]
THE PERSON I NEED IS MYTHO.
BUT THE ONE MYTHO NEEDS IS...
PRINCESS TUTU.
-I WONDER WHAT IT IS
I THINK OF YOU, FAKIR.
-WHEN I THINK OF RUE,
WHEN I THINK OF YOU, FAKIR,
AND WHEN I'M THINKING ABOUT
PRINCESS TUTU,
EACH ONE MAKES ME FEEL
DIFFERENT.
I'VE CHOSEN TO GO, FAKIR.
-YOU'RE KIDDING, RIGHT?
-I MEAN IT.
-WHAT POINT IS THERE?
-MAYBE THERE'S SOMETHING
SHE CAN TELL ME ABOUT TUTU.
-MYTHO'S CHANGING INTO...
A MYTHO THAT I DON'T KNOW.
-THAT IS SOMETHING
THAT CANNOT BE HELPED.
THE WAY WE THINK ABOUT THINGS
IS WORLDS APART.
-[ CHEWING ]
-AS YOU CAN SEE, EVEN WHAT
WE EAT IS QUITE DIFFERENT.
IT IS FOR THESE REASONS THAT
I DO NOT WISH TO MARRY YOU.
AND SO I'VE NO INTENTION
OF CHANGING MY WILL!
-[ GASPS ] MY WILL.
-DO YOU UNDERSTAND ME NOW,
MISS GOATETTE?
-[ BLEATS ]
[ BIRDS CHIRPING ]
[ PENCIL SCRAPING ]
-UM, HELLO?
-YOU'RE ONE OF
THE BALLET STUDENTS.
-WELL, I'M REALLY PRETTY
TERRIBLE AT DRAWING PICTURES.
-THAT'S BECAUSE
YOU'RE IN BALLET.
-I'M BAD AT BALLET, TOO, THOUGH.
-OH! YOU ARE? I'M SORRY!
-NO, NO, IT'S FINE.
MIND IF I TAKE A PEEK?
-WOW, IT'S GREAT!
A DRAWING OF RUE.
I'M SO JEALOUS OF YOU.
OH. DID YOU DRAW
THESE ONES, TOO?
-MM-HMM.
-HANG ON.
THEY'RE ALL DRAWINGS OF RUE?
WELL, RUE REALLY IS PRETTY,
SO I CAN TOTALLY UNDERSTAND.
HEY, THIS ONE'S SIGNED.
YOUR NAME IS MALEN?
HEY, THAT'S A CUTE NAME!
MY NAME'S DUCK!
-I DON'T UNDERSTAND.
-HUH?
-I DON'T...REALLY UNDERSTAND IT,
MYSELF.
I MEAN, I'VE ALWAYS ENJOYED
DOING LIFE DRAWING
WITH MISS RUE AS THE MODEL,
BUT IT USED TO BE I WANTED
TO DRAW OTHER THINGS, TOO,
LIKE FRUITS AND SCENERIES.
-OH.
-BUT NOW
I CAN ONLY DRAW MISS RUE.
-[ Thinking ] PRINCESS TUTU?
PRINCESS TUTU
WILL CHANGE EVERYTHING.
SHE'LL CHANGE MYTHO.
AT THIS RATE, MYTHO WILL ONLY
GROW MORE DISTANT FROM ME.
I WON'T ALLOW THAT TO HAPPEN.
-THEN WHAT DO YOU PLAN
TO DO ABOUT IT?
[ CLACKING ]
-[ GASPS ]
WHAT?
-A BEAUTIFUL BLACK SWAN.
-WHO IS THE HEROINE
OF THIS STORY?
IS IT PRINCESS TUTU
OR IS IT PRINCESS KRAEHE?
-PRINCESS KRAEHE THE HEROINE?
-IT HURTS WHEN I TRY
TO DRAW ANYTHING ELSE.
[ CHIME ]
-OH.
-A STORY DOESN'T NEED
TWO HEROINES NOW, DOES IT?
AND NO PRINCE NEEDS
TWO PRINCESSES.
NOW COME AND TELL ME
WHAT SHOULD HAPPEN NEXT.
[ CHIMING ]
[ BUBBLING ]
[ TINKLING ]
-[ CRYING ]
-PLEASE, COME DANCE WITH ME,
MISS MALEN.
-WHO ARE YOU?
I DON'T KNOW HOW TO DANCE.
-DON'T WORRY.
JUST DANCE FREELY.
-[ GASPS ]
-THE SOURCE OF YOUR PAIN
IS THE FALSE HEART
RESIDING IN YOUR HEART.
I'LL REMOVE IT FOR YOU.
THEN, ONCE AGAIN, YOU'LL BE ABLE
TO DRAW WHAT YOU LOVE.
-REALLY?
-YES.
YOU CAN GO BACK TO BEING
YOUR OLD SELF.
-THANK YOU. I'M SO GLAD.
[ HUMMING ]
[ MUSSORGSKY'S
"IL VECCHIO CASTELLO" PLAYING ]
-I JUST WANT TO STAY THE SAME,
NEVER CHANGING.
[ RAVENS CAWING, WINGS FLUTTER ]
[ CAWS ]
-YES, ONCE AGAIN,
PRINCESS TUTU...
HAS CHANGED MYTHO.
[ WIND GUSTS ]
[ WIND GUSTING ]
-AAH!
NO!
[ SCREAMING ]
[ RAVENS CAWING ]
-WHAT'S THIS?
-TUTU, WHERE ARE YOU?
HUH?
-WHAT EMOTION ARE YOU?
-I'M THE FEELING OF DEVOTION.
-YOU ARE A SHARD OF
THE PRINCE'S HEART
WHICH HE LOST.
[ WIND BLOWS ]
-SO THE FEELING OF DEVOTION,
IS IT?
-KRAEHE.
-I WILL NOT SUFFER YOU
TO RETURN SUCH A THING TO MYTHO.
-WHAT WILL YOU DO?
-I DON'T KNOW.
WHAT SHOULD I DO?
[ RAVENS CAWING ]
-[ GASPS ]
-[ GASPS ] NO!
[ WIND GUSTS ]
-AH!
[ GROANS ]
-[ LAUGHS ]
YOU HAD BETTER FORGET
ABOUT RESTORING
ANY MORE HEART SHARDS
TO THE PRINCE.
-BUT THE PRINCE TOLD ME.
THE PRINCE TOLD ME THAT
HE WANTS TO REGAIN HIS HEART!
-HMM?
[ GROANS ]
-PRINCESS TUTU.
I FINALLY FOUND YOU.
[ GASPS ]
KRAEHE.
-[ GASPS ]
WHY DO YOU LOOK AT ME THAT WAY?
AM I...
[ GASPS ]
-AM I...[ CRYING ]
-KRAEHE.
[ CHIMING ]
-[ CRYING ]
-WHAT'S WRONG?
-STAY AWAY!
[ SOBBING ]
-[ Thinking ]
AM I...NOT NEEDED?
-KRAEHE, WHY ARE YOU
IN SUCH PAIN?
-WHAT?
-IS THERE ANY WAY
I CAN HELP YOU?
-WHO IS KRAEHE?
[ GLASS SHATTERS ]
-[ GASPS ]
-FAKIR!
[ GLASS SHATTERS ]
-BE GONE, YOU UGLY CROW!
-CROW?
-[ CHUCKLES ]
THAT'S RIGHT, I AM A CROW.
AND I, ALONE,
AM THE TRUE PRIMA DONNA
PRINCESS KRAEHE.
I'LL TAKE WHAT I DESIRE
BY FORCE IF NEED BE.
[ RAVENS CAWING ]
[ RITSUKO OKAZAKI'S "ALTHOUGH
MY LOVE IS SMALL" PLAYING ]
-♪ YUME MIRU ♪
♪ YOU NI ♪
♪ KOI O SHITA NO ♪
♪ FUKURAMU ♪
♪ KOKORO GA FUKURAMU NO YO ♪
♪ IKITERUTTE SUTEKI
NA KOTO TO OMOTTA ♪
♪ ASU GA MACHI DOOSHII ♪
♪ MM ♪
♪ ANATA NO CHIKARA NI NARITAI
NO DONNA TOKI NI MO WATASHI ♪
♪ MATTE MATTE
KURENAI HASHITTE ♪
♪ HASHITTE IKU NO YO ♪
♪ KAZE MO AMAGUMO
MO OIKOSHITE ♪
♪ WATASHI DAKE
NO TSUBASA HABATAITE ♪
-MYTHO AND KRAEHE'S WEDDING?
WITH FAKIR FOR A WITNESS?
-THE LEGEND YOU TOLD ME ABOUT
AS A CHILD
IS SWIFTLY BECOMING REALITY.
YOU'D BE MUCH BETTER OFF
FORGETTING THIS ACCURSED TALE.
"PRINCE" IS A WEIRD NAME.
HOW 'BOUT WE CALL YOU MYTHO?
-ARE YOU GOING TO KRAEHE?
-I FEEL I MUST RUN AWAY.
-WHAT SAY YOU, PRINCESS TUTU?
AREN'T WE JUST PERFECT
FOR EACH OTHER?
-ALL WHO LOVE STORIES,
GATHER 'ROUND.
[ LAUGHS EVILLY ]