♪
( Menthuthuyoupi yawns )
Hmm?
( Grunts )
♪
( Singing in Japanese )
Narrator:
Upon entering the palace,
killua’s first thought was...
Killua: I knew it.
Narrator:
That was what he thought.
Instead of feeling pitou’s en
as they expected,
they found only youpi,
who wasn’t supposed to be
on the first floor,
standing
right in front of them.
Experience enabled killua
to remain calm
when faced with this situation,
which, despite their extensive
planning discussions,
had never come up.
Menthuthuyoupi:
Who are these guys?
Where did they come from?
Narrator: Youpi was faced
with an implausible situation
of his own,
but he simply ceased
all thought processes.
( Menthuthuyoupi growls )
♪
( Flesh crackling )
My body is a shield.
As long as I stand,
the king will be safe.
Narrator:
As a magical beast hybrid,
he was the only nonhuman
hybrid among the guards.
Perhaps because of this,
he cared less
about his individual identity
than the other two.
This lack of ego
became strength.
♪
Youpi smiled belligerently
and began transforming as shoot
stood frozen in his tracks.
( Menthuthuyoupi chuckles )
Narrator:
It wasn’t because shoot
found himself
psychologically defeated.
He knew...
Shoot: If I move
any closer to him than this,
he’ll strike,
and his attack could hit
knuckle and meleoron,
who I can only presume
are up ahead.
Narrator: But just
as he was preparing
to let loose
his flying hands and cage
to attract youpi’s attention
to himself,
it came.
Shoot: Huh?
( Killua gasps )
Wait. This is the dragon dive.
So netero’s friend was...
Narrator: Only killua
understood what was happening,
and it froze him on the spot.
Being ignorant, the shock
for the others was much greater.
Of them, there were only two.
Gon and youpi thought of nothing
but the enemy they faced.
Morel: No way.
Shoot: Has he lost it?
Killua: Your target isn’t youpi.
No. Hold on.
( Footsteps echoing )
♪
Narrator: To killua,
the realization came
only a moment later.
The others followed soon after.
Killua: Seriously?
How in the hell
did he realize that?
And so quickly
in a situation like this?
Narrator:
Although highly unlikely,
if meleoron and knuckle
were to be pierced
by the dragon’s arrows
while god’s accomplice
was in play
and, as a result,
died instantly,
would they cease
to be invisible?
Or, as nen is known
to intensify after death,
would their bodies
simply rot and decay
without ever being found?
No one knew the answer.
Assuming the latter,
even confirming
whether they were still alive
would be all but impossible.
That meant that,
in the worst-case scenario,
someone else would
have to take on youpi.
Shoot: That should have
been my job.
Gon!
Morel: It’s not shoot’s fault.
Even I didn’t realize it
as quickly as killua did.
Don’t blame yourself,
all right?
Pull yourself together.
If gon and killua take youpi,
then pitou falls to you.
♪
Narrator: However,
at that moment,
shoot was experiencing
a completely different emotion.
Shoot: Gon! I want to scream it
to the entire world!
That’s gon!
He’s so much younger than me,
and still, I owe him everything!
More than anything,
I feared facing danger,
even opportunity.
I locked myself
inside a cage to feel safe,
muffling even my own words
so that no one could hurt me.
I despised myself,
but I couldn’t fix it.
Friends and teachers
gave me advice,
but I brushed it off,
’cause they didn’t have
those fears themselves.
They were strong.
But somehow...
The one who managed
to break me out of my cage
was a young boy whose strength
can’t hold a candle to mine.
Narrator:
All of this was true.
Shoot did indeed
shy away from everything.
Shoot: I will survive this
so I can thank you.
Narrator: What shoot
failed to realize
was that whenever he’d
been faced with adversity,
that’s when he truly
came into his own.
Morel: All right.
( Menthuthuyoupi growls )
( Gon gasps )
Menthuthuyoupi: Hmm?
( Groans )
- ( Hunters gasping )
- ( Gon grunts )
Morel and shoot:
Knuckle and meleoron...
Killua and gon:
Are alive!
♪
Menthuthuyoupi: What?!
Who the hell just attacked me?
I didn’t see it.
Did they throw something?
Was it in my blind spot?
Knuckle: Hakoware, activate.
Narrator: Of course
they verified beforehand
that hakoware:
Bankruptcy chapter seven
would work
with god’s accomplice.
As long as god’s accomplice
was in play,
youpi would be
unable to see a.P.R.,
so it was reasonable enough
for them to expect youpi
to question
what had just happened
rather than concentrate
on the enemies in front of him.
Menthuthuyoupi:
I don’t sense any damage,
which means my focus
right now should be...
Narrator: So far, everything had
proceeded according to plan,
but even though knuckle
succeeded in landing a blow,
he felt a chill
run down his spine.
( Knuckle gasps )
Is this for real?
His aura is unlimited!
♪
Narrator: A veteran
of over 5,000 battles,
knuckle could quantify
his opponent’s power
based on his experience
and instinct,
and encountering a foe
with unprecedented powers
wasn’t even
a rare event for him.
But there was
no comparing the monster
that stood before him
with immense amounts of aura
to that of the countless
opponents he had faced before.
( Knuckle sputters )
Five times that of morel?
Ten times? More?
( Scoffs ) I can’t tell.
Narrator: This experience
was new to him.
( Knuckle groaning )
All right, let’s say
he’s ten times stronger,
with 700,000 aura.
Sure, he’d go bankrupt
eventually,
but how long would that take?
Neferpitou: Sire!
Narrator: Just then...
The extermination team
felt pitou’s ominous aura
as it enveloped them all.
That momentary hesitation
was not lost on youpi.
Shaiapouf: Sire!
Sire!
( Gasps )
♪
( Gasping )
Narrator:
Since pitou lacked wings,
the only option
was to drop straight down.
However, in this instance,
that may actually
have been fortunate.
Had the option been available,
pitou would certainly have
rushed straight toward the king,
just as pouf did.
This is a royal guard’s
natural response
when the king is threatened.
Given the circumstances,
it’s unlikely that pitou
would have had
the presence of mind to use en.
As a result...
Neferpitou: The guest’s quarters
are on the second floor
of the west tower.
There. The king is
with the blind woman.
( Gasps )
( Shudders )
They’re also using en
to locate the king!
Narrator: And it was then,
in that very moment, that pitou
realized the true gravity
of their situation.
In an instant, pitou crouched,
just as the four-legged
ancestors had done,
upper legs hard as steel
and swelled to twice
the size they had been
during the battle with kite...
All in order to reach the king
before the intruders could.
But only a second later...
( Neferpitou gasps )
♪
Narrator: The destination
pitou was traveling toward
began to emanate
negative energy.
It was so strong that pitou
immediately regretted
this decision.
Neferpitou:
This is the king’s.
Narrator: The aura coming
from the king was so unguarded
that his current state of mind
was quite easy to deduce.
As a result,
pitou was painfully aware
that the course of events
was heading
unimaginably and dramatically
in the wrong direction.
The central staircase
came crashing down.
( Rumbling )
♪
When the king looked away,
time suddenly
began to move again.
But all besides the king
were still frozen in time.
♪
Even those who broke in
to assassinate the king
stood in place,
breath catching in their throats
at the sight before them,
a young girl covered in blood.
She rested in the arms
of a grotesque creature,
who, despite his appearance,
held her in a way
that could only be described
as gentle and kind.
King: Pitou.
( Neferpitou gasps ) Sire?
Narrator: The expression
on the king’s face
had returned to normal.
This only increased
pitou’s uneasiness.
King: You will heal komugi.
I’m counting on you.
♪
Narrator: Through all of this,
the two veterans
continued to stand in silence,
watching their enemies closely
as an expression of respect.
What was unfolding was an act
of love for another’s life.
An intrusion at this point
would mean the complete loss
of all of their justification
and humanity.
Zeno: You know this isn’t
what you told me
I was signing up for.
Narrator:
Zeno’s rebuke was just,
and netero couldn’t help
but feel the same way.
King: Not here.
We should do this
somewhere else.
I believe a change of venue...
Would benefit you two as well.
Narrator: Netero had spent
a great deal of money
to enlist zeno’s help
in order to separate the king
from the royal guards.
He had no reason to object
to the king’s proposal.
However...
Netero: Yes. Fine.
Narrator: He could
not shake the feeling
that he was missing something
in this encounter.
Neferpitou: Dr. Blythe.
Narrator: The moment that
pitou’s ability was activated...
♪
It distracted the two men
for a split second,
a distraction for which
one could not blame them...
And right then,
the king calmly and easily
passed between them without
the slightest hint of fear.
♪
Their opponent was
an even greater monster.
( Singing in Japanese )