Kiriko father:
Once someone opens the door,
follow whatever directions
they give you.
♪
It was a lot of fun.
Now good luck to you.
( Killua grunts )
Yeah, thanks.
( Doorbell rings )
Hey, does someone
named mihael live here?
Mihael: Go do some shopping
at dick sakura by the station.
Use this card at the checkout.
Clerk: Very good, sir.
Please follow me this way.
( Elevator dings )
♪
( Singing in Japanese )
( Soft chatter )
Killua: There’s a lot
more people than last year.
Wonder if there’s
anybody I know.
Brothers: Hey.
Umori: You walked
all over us last year.
Imori: But it’s gonna be
a lot different this time.
Amori: We all put ourselves
through some intense training
after what happened.
Brothers:
Now our teamwork’s perfect,
so good luck trying to--
( brothers gasp )
Examiner:
Thanks for coming, everyone!
- Killua: Hmm.
- Examiner: This year,
1,489 applicants
have made it this far,
but the examiner
for the second phase
asked me to trim
that number down to about 300.
But as for the exam itself,
lunch is two hours away,
so knock out five people
before then.
( All gasp )
Examiner:
Once all five are down,
grab their badges,
and come see me.
I’ll be right on the other side
of the door.
All right. As soon as it closes,
that’s your cue to get started.
( All yelling )
Examiner: Every phase
of the exam should be like this.
A hunter’s gotta be strong,
and this helps find
and weed out the weaklings.
( Blows landing )
Zepile: Huh?
Killua: You’re here,
too, old man?
Zepile: Killu--( Groans )
Killua: Sucks for you.
I’ll pass this year,
and just me.
Amori: He’s totally
out of our league.
Imori: That kid was born
to be a top-rate hunter.
Umori: This’ll be our last year
trying out for the hunter exam.
( Body falls )
- ( Door opens )
- Examiner: Eh?
Took you long enough.
It’s already been
a full hour and a half.
What are the others doing?
Killua: They’re all asleep.
Examiner: Huh?
Killua: It just took me
a little while
to collect all the badges.
( Examiner gasps )
Killua: What now? Second phase?
( Netero laughs )
That won’t be necessary,
i’m afraid.
He’s already demonstrated
his skill quite sufficiently.
Killua,
inhabitant of the shadows.
He’s certainly matured
since we saw him last.
Examiner:
Applicant 1,219, killua.
Killua: Here.
Examiner: Congratulations!
You passed!
♪
( Gon gasps )
Welcome back, killua!
How was it?
Killua: Well, I aced it
in no time, naturally.
Both: Yeah!
Bisky: I’m sorry
to interrupt your celebration,
but take a look
at these spell cards.
Killua: Oh, wow!
There’s even an s-rank card.
So how much do you think
we can sell it for?
Bisky: I’m not sure, but why
don’t we go and ask around?
Gon: No.
We should use it wisely.
( Bisky growls )
Gon: So what do
you think, killua?
Killua: I guess
it’s safe to hold on to it.
It’s not gonna get stolen
with all these defensive spells.
Have you guys tried
any of these out yet?
Gon:
Just the blackout curtain one.
Killua: Why only one?
Why even have ’em
if you don’t use ’em?
Here.
Start off by using this one.
It lets you choose
any player you’ve met
and have a talk with them.
Gon: Who should we talk to?
Killua: First,
let’s look at who’s available.
Gon: All right. Contact on!
Killua: I didn’t know
there’d be so many.
( Gasps )
Hey, when’d you run into him?
Gon: Huh?
( Gasps )
Chrollo?!
Bisky: Hold on. Who’s chrollo?
Gon: I haven’t seen him.
Well, not inside of the game,
anyway.
Killua: Does that mean
you passed each other
without noticing?
Bisky: What are
you two talking about?
Gon: But I don’t get it.
I could have sworn kurapika
sealed his nen, didn’t he?
Killua: He sure did,
and you have to use nen
just to get inside the game.
Bisky: Who is this kurapika?
Gon: If that’s the case,
then that means--
bisky: Come on! What the hell
are you guys talking about?!
( Shalnark laughs )
Oh, I get it now.
That’s what’s going on.
( Laughs )
Franklin: It isn’t funny.
Just explain to us
what’s happening.
Shalnark: Sorry about that.
This probably isn’t the boss.
He hasn’t exorcised
the nen from his body.
Bisky: Exorcism?
It’s quite possible.
- Killua: It is?
- Bisky: Of course.
If you’re able
to place nen on others,
there would have to a way
to remove it as well.
Killua: So does that mean that
chrollo removed kurapika’s nen
and then entered the game?
Gon: Why would he come here?
Killua: I’ve got no idea,
but we should probably
let kurapika know.
In that case, i’m gonna
hop out of the game again.
Gon: Why don’t you use
a spell card to leave?
Killua: Hold on to it.
I’ll be back in four hours.
( Shalnark laughs ) I should
have realized it sooner.
Fact is, this island is due east
of yorknew city, straight shot.
( All gasp )
Chrollo: Perhaps to the east,
one can be tracked.
The one most needed,
you’re sure to find
phinks: I see.
The boss came to find
someone to exorcise that nen.
Shalnark: He probably arrived
here the same way we did,
but then razor kicked him out.
I assume that’s when he realized
this was greed island.
But now that the boss
can’t use nen anymore,
he can’t enter
through the usual channels,
so he must have hired someone
to come to the island for him,
and he had them use his name
as a hidden message
for the rest of us.
Chrollo: The exorcist
is on greed island.
( Phinks laughs )
Another change in plans, huh?
Let’s bring
everybody else out here.
Franklin: I agree.
Then all of us
will look for the exorcist.
Hisoka: One small correction.
- Shalnark: Huh?
- ( Franklin gasps )
♪
Phinks: It’s you.
Shalnark: Hisoka!
Hisoka: See, using chrollo’s
name was actually my idea,
but I didn’t know that entering
any name you like was an option,
or at least, not until I had
already gotten inside.
You should be praising
my initiative.
If not for me,
you never would have understood
chrollo’s message.
Phinks: So that’s what this
is all about, huh?
I’ve got half a mind
to kill you right here and now,
but i’ll leave that to the boss.
( Hisoka chuckles )
Well, if I can help further,
use contact to find me,
and i’ll let you know if I
happen to learn anything new.
So long.
Shizuku: I didn’t think the boss
would have hired hisoka.
Guess he didn’t have
much of a choice, but still...
Franklin: I’m betting
that he offered him
a duel post-exorcism.
Shalnark: Probably, but now
it’s only a matter of time
until the boss comes back.
Kurapika: I doubt it.
If he or one
of the other spiders
were to attempt
to remove my nen,
I would know
about it immediately.
There’s no other way around it.
Killua: So when you
set up your ability,
you took something
like this into account?
Kurapika: Of course I did.
If you’re able
to place nen on others,
it stands to reason
that the ability to remove it
exists as well.
It’s common sense.
( Killua groans ) Well,
just thought i’d let you know.
You can do
whatever you want with it.
Kurapika: I appreciate that.
You have my gratitude.
( Hangs up )
( Knock on door )
( Door opens )
Did you need anything?
( Nostrade crying )
What am I supposed to do?
What will I do this month?
Please, tell me.
What should I do now?
Kurapika: It’s going
to be all right.
Just let me handle--
nostrade: What do
you know about it?!
What the hell good are you
if you have no idea what’s
gonna happen in the future?
Neon, I need her!
Restore her at once!
( Sobbing )
Damn it!
How could this have happened?!
( Pen clicking )
Neon: I wonder what’s wrong.
Why did it stop coming out
all of a sudden?
Killua: See ya!
♪
Well, it looks like it’s not
the real chrollo lucilfer.
Gon: Wait. It’s not?
Killua: Talked to kurapika.
He was pretty calm about it.
By the way he responded,
he didn’t sound concerned.
Bisky: It sounds like you got
all worked up over nothing.
Now, if you ask me,
you should get back
to focusing on yourselves.
Gon: Osu! Start with the basics!
Bisky: We’re not going to train.
We’ve gotten distracted,
but it’s time we start trying
to beat this game!
( Giggles )
Man: It’s said
that the legendary
king white stag beetle
lives only in this tree
and that there’s
only one way to capture it,
hit the tree and shake it out!
( Gon grunts )
Show me rock!
Jan Ken rock! Hah!
Killua: Oh, wow!
Bisky: It’s raining bugs
everywhere!
Gon: Found it!
Difficulty rank a!
All right! That makes three
king white stag beetle cards!
Killua: You know,
you could have gotten more
if you’d just thrown
a real punch.
Gon: Yeah,
you’re probably right,
but I didn’t want
to damage the tree.
♪
Man #2: There is no such girl
here in this mansion.
And even if there were, you
would never be able to find her,
not with all the traps that you
would have to get past first.
- Killua: Found her!
- ( Man #2 gasps )
She was hidden in a room
deep underground.
Man #2: What?!
Damn you!
( Yells )
Killua: A gold dust girl,
rank a!
Gon: But the guard
was only an f-rank.
Bisky: Next let’s head
to dorias, the gambling town!
Gon: Ah, man!
The antokiba contest.
That’s supposed
to be today, right?
Killua: We’re passing through,
so let’s give it a try.
( Crowd cheering )
Announcer: The winner this month
is team killua and gon!
Both: A paladin’s necklace!
Score!
Gon: Hey, I don’t think I get
what this description means.
Killua: Let’s go ask
one of the shopkeepers.
Shopkeeper:
When you wear this necklace,
then you’re impervious.
It reflects
all of the attack spells
directed at you,
and that isn’t all.
If you find
that any of your cards
are under the effects of
either the clone or fake cards,
you can restore them
with a touch.
Killua: Hear that?
If we wear this,
we won’t have to worry
about losing any cards!
♪
Gon: Okay, memory helmet,
witch’s love potion,
risky dice,
king white stag beetle,
gold dust girl,
and paladin’s necklace--
a total of six different
specified-slot cards!
Boys: Piece of cake, huh?
Bisky: Piece of cake?
Not at all.
This was only possible because
of your grueling training.
- ( Book chimes )
- Both: Huh?
Book: Attention. Another player
has cast contact on you.
Player: Hey, gon.
It’s been a while.
Gon: Who are you?
( Player chuckles )
What, you don’t remember me?
Well, what about the player who
took the sword of truth from you
in antokiba? Remember him?
( Boys gasp )
Gon: What do you want?
Player: Up for a trade?
I have number 66,
the witch’s diet pills,
and 27. That one is
the book of v.I.P. Passes.
You can talk it over
with your friends.
Gon: What do you think?
♪
( Book chimes )
Book: Attention. Another player
has cast contact on you.
Tsezgerra: Tsezguerra here.
Genthru: Oh, you again, huh?
Tsezgerra: Interested in trading
your angel’s breath
for our patch of forest?
It’s an ss-rank card.
Genthru: Yeah, no, thanks.
As i’ve already said,
I have no desire
to deal with you.
Tsezgerra: What if
I throw in a clone?
Genthru: I thought I made it
clear there’s no deal here.
You already have
92 different cards.
All that’s left are the ones
monopolized
by the other players.
Isn’t that right?
Tsezgerra: Actually we have 95.
Genthru: I’m sure
you have some of the items
and you’re waiting for someone
else to use gain on them.
In fact, it’s entirely possible
that angel’s breath is the last
card that you need to obtain,
and I can’t think
of a single reason
we would give that to you and
lose the game in the process.
( Tsezgerra chuckles )
Stop playing dumb.
I happen to know
that you and your people
are currently monopolizing
both angel’s breath
and night Jade, which means
the game is not over yet.
Genthru: Oh?
I wish you boys
the best of luck,
but we’re never going
to let you have these cards.
Tsezgerra: And if I offer three?
The patch of forest,
spirited away hollow,
and then to top it all off,
there’s miniature dragon.
And you only have
to give us night Jade,
not angel’s breath.
We’d be giving you one ss-rank
and two s-rank,
while you’d only
give up an a-rank.
That’s too good to pass up.
Genthru: We’ll need
a little time to discuss it.
Tsezgerra: To be clear,
this is our final offer.
We won’t negotiate any further.
Genthru: Book.
Sub: It’s gotta be a trap.
It’s too good to be true.
Genthru: Tsezguerra
is awfully cautious.
I doubt he’s looking
to pick a fight with us.
But that said, he’s not the type
to make a losing deal, either.
Which must mean he thinks
he can obtain
an angel’s breath on his own.
Bara: What do you think?
I mean, there are
40 types of spell cards.
Does he have all of them?
Genthru: Maybe. If so,
they’re just waiting for us
to use gain on one
of our angel’s breaths.
Sub: Could be,
but it took
a whole lot of hard work
to monopolize night Jade.
If one of the cards
got destroyed,
one of our Jade jewels
would turn back into a card.
Those guys might be able
to get their hands on an ss-rank
angel’s breath,
but the a-rank night Jade is
a lot harder for them to get.
Genthru: This is a real gamble.
Player: Book.
See ya.
( Gon sighs )
Bisky: That was
surprisingly uneventful.
Killua: It was kind of
a letdown, actually.
Gon: I was so nervous,
but that’s seven types
in just three days!
We’re making real progress.
Killua: Okay! Let’s keep it up!
Are there any other events for
getting restricted-slot cards?
Bisky: Uh, I think there are,
but let me see.
Gon: Prizes from the slots?
Killua: Well, it is
the city of gambling.
Bisky: You have
a .01% chance of winning.
That’s just one in 10,000.
Killua: So it all
comes down to luck.
That’s pretty risky.
I know!
Hey, gon, use that dice!
Now, if we get great luck,
we can win.
Gon: But if you roll worst luck,
something so bad’s gonna happen
that’ll it’ll cancel out
everything good
that’s happened to us.
Killua: Yeah, but there’s only
a one-in-20 chance
of that, right?
Hah.
Yes!
All we gotta do
is spin the wheel!
♪
Wow!
Awesome! First try!
I scored a rainbow diamond!
It’s just like I thought.
This little die is the key
to really hitting it big-time
in this city!
Bisky: But what if
you roll worst luck?
Things could get really scary
really quickly.
Killua: Don’t worry about it.
It’s not like it’s
gonna kill me, right?
- ( Explosion )
- Bisky: Huh?
Player: Oh, no!
A slot machine exploded!
Player #2: I knew
something was wrong.
That guy just hit the jackpot
five times in a row.
Player #3: And he
was acting weird.
He kept rolling
some funny-looking die.
Player #1: Whoa!
His face is mush! Look!
Bara: Okay, so my vote
is that we make the trade.
Sub: Yeah. We want
all s-rank cards and above,
and the sooner we obtain them,
the better.
Genthru: True,
but as for a-rank and below...
♪
( Men gasping )
Genthru: Roll.
Player: Please spare me.
I’m begging you!
Genthru: Don’t worry.
It’s only your third time.
You’ll be all right.
Player: But I knew a guy,
and he had the worst luck
on his first roll, and he died!
Spare me!
If I roll worst luck,
that means i’ll be hit
for every time the other players
rolled great luck!
Genthru: That’s not my problem.
Roll it.
Or perhaps
you’d rather die now.
( Player whimpering )
Oh, please.
( Sighs )
Genthru: There. See?
It’s pretty rare
to get worst luck.
Now we’ll use the lottery card.
Sub: We want number 75,
the wild luck alexandrite.
You got that?
And if you’re able to obtain
one for us, we’ll set you free.
Player: Please. Oh, please!
Lottery on!
Sub: Well?
Number 76. Ooh, so close.
I guess today’s
not your lucky day.
Bara: Right! One more! Roll!
Bombers: One more time!
One more time!
Time to see
what motaricke’s got!
It’s time to shine
just one more time!
( Genthru scoffs )
So it didn’t happen, huh?
Bara: Well, what now, gen?
Should we make
the first move or what?
Genthru: Like I said,
combat is our last resort.
- It’s still early.
- Sub: Hold on.
We’re trying to stay
one step ahead of them, right?
But as soon as we commit,
further negotiations
will be completely impossible.
Genthru: What do you
have in mind?
Sub: We use
tax collector’s gauntlet
combined with risky dice.
♪
Genthru: I understand.
You’re saying we use that
to steal eight cards
from them immediately,
but that’d
definitely be dangerous.
If someone rolls worst luck,
then they’ll probably die,
and this job is
too important to leave to them.
Bara: Come on!
Sub: We’ve come this far!
Let’s clear the game!
Bara: Hey, gen,
what are you doing?
Genthru:
I’ve told you this before.
When we take a big risk like
this one, we share the danger.
( Both gasp )
( Both sigh )
( Book chimes )
Tsezgerra: It’s tsezguerra.
What’ll it be?
Genthru: We’re in.
You have yourself a deal.
( Chuckles )
( Killua groans )
I’m gonna do it.
Just one more time!
I already said i’m gonna do it,
so i’m gonna do it!
( Groans )
Bisky: All right!
On to the next city! Let’s go!
♪
Narrator: Gon and
the rest of his team
have begun working
to beat the game.
The story’s climax
is drawing near.
( Singing in Japanese )