♪
Cheetu: Well, well,
i guess you guys
were lying in wait for me.
Sorry, but that’s
gonna backfire on you.
You’re gonna die
without ever getting
the chance to strike back.
( Knuckle laughs )
oh, yeah?
Cheetu: Hmm?
Knuckle: I barely felt a thing.
With a punch like that,
you could hit us
a few thousand times more
and still not kill us.
( Cheetu laughs )
okay, I get it.
You’re just trying to act tough.
( Knuckle growls )
( Cheetu laughs )
the strike’s
already been called,
and you’re still swinging.
( Laughs )
just a warning.
I’ve been holding back.
I can run faster
and punch harder.
That’s a surprise.
He actually aimed
accurately at my face.
I was certain that he couldn’t
follow my motion earlier.
Was it a lucky guess?
( Knuckle groans )
Cheetu: Huh? Him, too?!
He’s tracking where i’m
going to be before he attacks.
I’ve only just encountered them,
and they’ve adjusted to my speed
that quickly?
They’re nothing like the guys
from yesterday.
How fun! Makes it worthwhile
playing with your food!
( Morel groans )
♪
( Singing in Japanese )
( Knuckle and moral groaning )
( Cheetu laughs )
Minds quicker than your bodies?
you obviously
can’t compete physically,
so how are you
gonna compensate?
With guns or numbers?
( Knuckle chuckles )
With our wits and experience.
♪
( Morel exhales )
Cheetu: Huh?
Where did this stuff come from?
Is it smoke? Sleeping gas?
Or maybe poison?
No. They’re standing in it, too.
This must be some kind
of special ability.
( Morel chuckles )
Are you scared?
Run away if you want to.
( Cheetu laughs )
Does that mean that you’re
not running away, then?
So it’s a smoke screen.
They’ll use it as cover
for their attack.
Well, let’s see
what they’ve got.
Here it comes!
( Gasps )
( Groans )
Knuckle: When you’re startled,
your whole body freezes up.
This trick won’t always work
on the same opponent,
but once is enough.
Cheetu: Are you sure?
’cause that didn’t hurt.
I admit you caught me
a bit off guard,
but even so, i’m perfectly fine.
Huh?
What the hell is this?
Knuckle: Gee, I wonder.
Cheetu: Huh?
A.p.r.: It is time.
You’ve accrued interest.
( A.p.r. Expands )
Cheetu: What is this?
Tell me!
morel: Well,
it looks like your anger
is binding you
to your surroundings,
which means sending you
tumbling will be easy.
( Cheetu growls )
Shut up!
They’re gone.
Where did you go?!
A.p.r.: It is time.
You have accrued interest.
( Cheetu gasps )
( Growls )
( Scoffs )
It doesn’t matter
what your power does.
I just have to leave you
in my dust!
morel: It looks like
he’s powerless against zetsu.
Knuckle: Well, keep in mind
we’re dealing with a newbie
or peon soldier ant.
with a.P.R. On him,
tracking him will be a breeze.
We’ll just chase him down,
box him in,
and that’ll be the end of it.
morel: But doesn’t
your ability lose its effect
if the target
moves too far away?
knuckle: Well, sure,
it’ll stop accruing interest,
but it won’t disappear.
Once i’m back in range,
the counter will start again.
Best part is, we won’t even
need to change it to I.R.S.
We’ve already seen
what he can do.
Morel: You damn fool.
Just because we know
his pitches doesn’t mean
that we don’t still run the risk
of being struck out.
I say we just leave him
for someone who’s
better equipped to handle him.
Knuckle: Yeah, you’re right.
We’ll focus on gon and killua.
( Cheetu panting )
Damn. I can’t shake
this stupid thing,
and if I can’t outrun it,
that means...
It must be nen.
I’m gonna need a lot more
than just speed here.
♪
( Footsteps echoing )
( Soft whooshing )
( Whooshing, clattering )
Shoot: Kite is inside this cage,
but he’s no longer
the person you once knew.
Gon: It’s okay.
We’re gonna find a way
to cure him somehow.
Shoot: Hotel rafflesia.
Once I deal a certain amount
of damage to my enemy,
the cage traps them inside,
either whole or just a part.
( Killua gasps )
So that’s how he took my eye.
- ( Gate squeaking )
- ( Gon gasps )
( Footsteps inside )
- ( Killua gasps )
- ( Gon gasps )
♪
( Energy whooshing )
Shoot: Once out,
he’ll return
to his original size.
Be careful.
He can’t use nen,
but he’s still
as strong as ever.
( Gon gasps )
Kite.
Knuckle: We have reason
to believe he was being used
as a training tool
for the soldier ants.
he mechanically attacks
anything that gets close to him.
( Slow footsteps echoing )
Gon: Kite, you’re safe.
Everything’s gonna be okay now.
♪
( Killua gasps )
Gon: You haven’t hit me since--
since the day we first met.
I still remember the pain.
( Blows landing )
( Knuckle groans )
Morel: Well? Are you
gonna let this continue?
Gon can’t defend himself
with nen either, right?
Killua: It’ll be fine.
Gon is bound to notice.
In fact, he might have
figured it out already,
if we’re lucky.
Knov: Perhaps.
He’s suppressing his reflexes
to dodge or block,
allowing himself to be hit.
That much is painfully obvious.
Knuckle: For real?
Kite’s attacks may be robotic
and easy to anticipate,
but gon shouldn’t
be able to adapt
so quickly in his condition.
Killua: He just doesn’t know
what else to do.
I’m sure of it.
We created this reality,
and now we’ve gotta face it.
( Blows striking )
Gon: He’ll go right next.
Again.
Then left.
Then a feint.
( Gasps )
He really is like a machine.
Kite isn’t this weak.
His punches hurt more than this,
a lot more!
( Both gasp )
Gon: I’m so sorry.
You’re only like this
because of us.
You go ahead and get some rest.
You can leave everything to us.
( Gasps )
( Killua gasps )
♪
Knuckle: Level two.
Gon can’t see that thing,
but it activates
whenever someone touches kite.
You’re gonna need some seriously
advanced fighting skills
to defeat him now.
My ability sealed kite’s nen,
but that thing right there
is all the nen ability
of whoever’s controlling him.
be careful.
If you touch him again,
he’ll attack you relentlessly.
Gon: What do I do?
How am I gonna stop him?
Shoot: We were forced to
wound him badly, unfortunately.
i’m sorry.
We had no other choice.
If you keep away,
he won’t attack.
Gon: Kite, just hold on
a little longer.
I’ll fix you. I promise.
( Knuckle growls )
Gon: Killua...
i promise.
I’ll take ’em on myself.
( Door closes )
Knuckle: Killua...
i could tell
that something was different.
What did you two do?
You changed so much
in such a short time.
Killua: We didn’t do anything.
They’re the ones
who changed us.
narrator:
29 long days have passed
since gon first lost
the ability to use nen.
Morel: So what do you think?
was it right
to let them tag along?
We’ll be breaking our promise
to the old man, you know.
Knov: It’s not a problem.
The test was only intended
to determine who would
and would not enter the ngl,
and we are, at the moment,
headed to the Republic
of east gorteau.
Isn’t that correct?
Morel: Sure sounds like
you’re splitting hairs to me.
Knov: You’re not suggesting
we take them back, are you?
Morel: No. Those two
are full-grown tigers now,
and the best thing
about full-grown tigers
is they can take care
of themselves.
Shoot: Well, killua is capable.
Do you think gon is, too?
I must admit I was impressed
by the way he moved back there,
but I can’t say i’ve seen him
show any fire since then.
He’s improved with training,
but he clearly lacks
any real focus.
He’s inconsistent.
His power levels
can vary widely.
Morel: Maybe so, but at least
he’s consistently inconsistent.
he doesn’t take things
too seriously unless he has to.
I feel his lack of motivation
is like a coiled up spring.
Knuckle: How so?
Morel: He’s been saving up
all that energy...
Biding his time
’til he finds an enemy
he hates enough
to unleash it on.
Well, we’ll see soon enough.
Gon’s nen will be back tomorrow,
just in time,
and the enemy’s straight ahead.
( Sizzling )
Announcer: The question
that’s on everyone’s mind
is what these sudden changes
in east gorteau
could possibly mean.
Diego has personally invited
all the citizens in the country
to the capital city of peijing
to celebrate the nation’s
founding in just ten days.
Commentator: Yes, that’s right.
There have been times
when all citizens
were invited to participate,
but I can honestly say
that we’ve never seen
anything on this scale,
where practically every citizen,
from infants to the infirm,
have all been summoned
for a celebration
spanning three whole days.
i believe
it’s rather safe to assume
that this time around,
the goal must be different.
Announcer: And what do you
believe the goal might be?
Commentator: I can’t say. But if
he announced his successor
and abdication simultaneously,
it would send
a very powerful message.
Still, I find it hard to imagine
that Diego would voluntarily
relinquish his power.
There may be another matter this
is meant to draw attention from,
a distraction, if you will.
Announcer: Well, whatever it is,
in ten short days,
the whole world
will be watching.
In other news...
Morel: Colt has a theory.
he believes
that the celebration
will be used
to sort the population.
Knov: We don’t know
what they’ll do
to those found
to have awakened nen,
but 99% of the humans
that are there now
will most certainly die,
but we cannot let that happen.
We have ten days.
Killua: The old man,
what’s he up to right now?
Knov: He sent me a text
a little while ago
saying he’s already
infiltrated east gorteau.
I haven’t heard a word
from him since then.
Killua: So do you think
he’s been taken out?
Knov: Before he left, he told us
that if we don’t hear
from him today,
we’re to assume
the worst has happened.
( Cell phone rings )
( All gasp )
Knov: Hmph.
Speak of the devil.
It’s the chairman.
( Morel grunts )
that old man’s
got some satellites for ears.
Knov: He already
knows everything,
including the fact
that you’re here
and that morel is trashing him.
Netero: I want you
to split into three pairs
and lure the royal guards
away from the king.
start at midnight
the night before the rally.
From the old man
with satellite ears.
Morel: That old bastard
scares the crap out of me.
I.r.s.: Hate to say goodbye,
but unfortunately for me,
the 30 days are up meow,
and that means it’s time
for me to be moving on,
so see you later!
( Laughs )
( Gon gasps )
Knuckle: Well, all right.
it looks like
you can use nen again.
Go on. Try it out.
Morel: Gon...
Sorry, but i’m not convinced
we should keep you around.
( Killua and knuckle gasp )
Morel: Show me your resolve.
Pretend i’m the enemy
who did all that to kite.
if your attack
isn’t powerful enough,
i’ll call
for a replacement hunter.
knuckle: Wow.
Master can be such a headache.
He approved of him forever ago.
Gon, don’t hold back.
Show him your jajanken.
Gon: A real attack?
Morel: Yes, damn it!
Give me everything you’ve got,
or you’re off the team.
Gon: Got it.
( Morel inhales )
( Grunts )
♪
( Gasps )
Gon: Show me rock.
( Morel gasps )
( Gon panting )
Killua: Gon, that’s enough.
Am I right, old man?
Morel: Uh, yeah.
( Gon gasps )
Killua! Thanks a lot!
Uh, sorry, Mr. Morel.
i really was
just about to kill you.
( Morel gasps )
( Chuckles )
( Laughing )
you got me
real good there, kid.
And you’ve got just about
the right amount
of crazy in you, too.
Okay, we’ll split up now.
Go and fulfill your mission
by any means necessary.
Gon and killua will take
neferpitou, as requested.
knuckle and shoot
will take menthuthuyoupi.
Knov and I will take shaiapouf.
Best of luck out there.
Narrator: The preparations
for the final battle
are complete at last.
The Victor will be decided
in ten days.
♪
( Singing in Japanese )