♪
( Singing in Japanese )
Narrator:
With the death of king meruem,
the battle between chimera ants
and humans was finally over.
The Republic of east gorteau
and the ngl
were placed
under the provisional rule
of the international
security agency,
effectively dismantling
both countries.
Between the two former nations,
five million survivors
became refugees.
The mitene union’s
three remaining countries
divided east gorteau’s
assets equally
and, after brief negotiations,
agreed to have joint control
over the territory.
As for the ngl,
there was a proposal
to permanently designate
all uninhabited land
as a nature reserve,
in hopes that this
would prevent future conflict,
and it was quickly approved
in the international assembly.
It was also agreed
that the nature reserve
would be placed
under the jurisdiction
of the hunter association.
♪
Welfin: You sure about this?
Bloster: You bet.
I’m gonna live right here,
no question.
I don’t remember gyro,
but, still, this place
just feels like home.
It’s only a guess, but I
probably just lived in the ngl
and didn’t work for gyro.
Welfin: Well, i’m not
gonna twist your arm.
This is probably safer
than the other countries.
Bloster: No doubt about that.
Just one good look at me,
and the peacekeepers
would arrest me on the spot.
Welfin: I wonder...
Bloster: Hmm?
Welfin: Is that her deal, too?
It’d make sense.
Bloster: No. Her case is
a little bit different.
She’s a lot more
like you guys than me.
Welfin: Huh?
What are you talking about?
Hina: Hey!
Are you done?! Let’s get moving!
Welfin: She’s such a brat.
Just give me a minute!
Bloster: Anyways,
for someone like me
who has no memory
of my previous life,
those like you and hina,
who do remember,
you all seem a little,
I don’t know, different.
Maybe it’s
the light in your eyes
or how you look off
into the distance.
I can tell
just by looking at you,
like, yeah, "this guy
remembers his past."
And I can tell
she remembers, too.
It’s as plain as day.
Welfin: Huh.
Bloster: From what hina says,
she doesn’t talk very much.
( Hina sighs )
Bloster: But, you know, I don’t
think that she won’t talk.
It’s that she’s not able to.
She’s probably a little kid.
Hina: Hurry up, welfin,
or we’re just
gonna leave without you!
Welfin: Would you shut up?!
I’m on my way!
- Bloster: See ya.
- Welfin: Huh?
Bloster: We might not
see each other again,
so take care, okay?
Welfin: I will.
Just don’t die...
Until you’re dead.
Bloster: The hell is that?
Welfin: How gyro said goodbye.
It’s always been
my favorite phrase.
What, does it
ring a bell for you?
Bloster: No,
but I kinda like it.
Welfin: Oh, right.
Bloster: So it’s like
"seize the day," huh?
Welfin: Heh. Later.
Bloster: Yeah.
Okay, you wanna get going?
( Hina humming a tune )
Yay! We’re on the hunt.
Time to go find sir gyro.
That’s awesome!
Welfin: You really
don’t have any shame, do you?
Not long ago,
you were all, "sir hagya," this
and, "sir leol," that.
Hina: Wait. Do I know them?
Guess not.
Welfin: Huh?!
( Hina giggles )
No point in thinking
about the dead, right?
Keep looking forward.
Full speed ahead!
( Welfin sighs )
Well, anyway, are you positive
we can make it safely
through the harbor?
Bizeff: Yes.
It’s a government vehicle,
so i’ll show my card,
and they’ll let us pass.
( Sighs )
Before long,
i’ll be living in meteor city.
Oh, how far i’ve fallen.
Welfin: You don’t have to be
so negative, you know.
( Sighs )
Just a little bit longer to go.
I’m willing to bet
gyro’s heading there, too.
It’s possible
that he’s already gathered
all the people and tools
we’re gonna need,
so we’ll be set to start
building our own nation.
And you know what that means,
that we’re gonna be back on top
in no time at all!
Hina: Yay!
( Giggles )
Bizeff: Well, I envy
your unbridled optimism.
I just wish that I shared it.
Welfin: Optimism?
Got that right.
I mean, I died twice already,
and check it out.
I’m still alive.
There’s nothing left
to fear now. Bring it on!
( Bizeff sighs )
Welfin: Besides i’m the one
who stopped the king, remember?
- ( Hina giggles )
- Bizeff: Knock it off!
- ( Gasps )
- ( Both laughing )
Bizeff: Yes, you’re right.
I’m just a class-a
political criminal now.
Might as well enjoy
whatever’s next.
Welfin: Yeah, that’s the spirit.
It’s like I always say,
"don’t die ’til you’re dead."
Hina: Kinda goes
without saying, right?
Welfin: Shut up!
Narrator: And so,
welfin, hina, and bizeff
head to meteor city
in the hopes of finding gyro.
♪
Bloster: Is that
the village over there?
Hey, come on.
There’s no need to worry.
I’ll be by your side.
Woman: Hmm?
( Gasps )
( Screams ) Monster!
( Women screaming )
( Doors slam )
( Bloster sighs )
Well, I can’t blame ’em.
♪
Hey! People of the ngl!
I need someone
who can communicate
in a peaceful
and reasonable manner!
Please help us!
I promise, we mean you no harm!
I’ve got something
I need to ask you!
Woman: All right. Sounds like
you speak our language.
Tell us who you are.
Bloster: Uh, well...
This is going to be
pretty hard to believe.
I just ask that you hear me out.
♪
You’re the only ones
I can turn to.
( No audible dialogue )
( Mother gasps )
( Sighs )
( Crying )
( Gasps )
( Shidore gasps )
( Crying )
Mother: Reina?
Shidore: How did--
how did you know?
Mother: Oh, reina.
Reina! Reina!
( Sobs )
Shidore: How could you
tell it was me?
Mother: I’m your mother, reina.
Of course I could tell.
How could I not?
Welcome home.
I’m so glad that you’re back.
Shidore: Mommy, big--
big brother protected me.
He told the monster to go away,
and he told me to run.
He kept me safe.
If it hadn’t been for him--
but...
I was too scared to move.
I’m sorry!
( Sobbing )
Mother: It’s okay.
Don’t be sorry.
I know you and Kurt
did your best.
I’m the one who’s sorry,
sorry I wasn’t there with you,
sorry I couldn’t keep you safe.
( Both crying )
Woman: Reina, dear,
welcome back home.
You must be starving.
Woman #2: Why don’t we
all go eat together?
♪
( No audible dialogue )
- Woman #3: Hello.
- Bloster: Eh?
Woman #3: Would you
like to stay and join us?
Bloster: Eh, no.
Thanks, anyway.
Woman #3: Oh, please,
don’t be like that.
Reina, she owes you
her life, you know.
We want to thank you
for what you’ve done.
Bloster: Look, i’m not
that kinda guy, okay? See you.
Damn it.
Now we’re even. It’s over.
Damn that stupid octopus.
He never
should have let me live.
( Gasps )
Eh?
Reina: Thank you.
Come on.
Let’s go eat together.
( Bloster gasps )
Hey, what’s going on?
What is this?
Why am I crying?
Narrator: Reina and bloster,
home at last.
( Telephone ringing )
Morel: Hello. Colt? It’s me.
Looks like the politicians
have somehow turned this
into an international crisis.
Officially, the ants had nothing
to do with recent events.
Colt: We had
nothing to do with it?
I didn’t realize
they could do that.
Morel: They can.
That’s what politics
is all about.
You’ll be classified
as a new magical beast.
Colt: Is that right?
Morel: Just act the part
of a good magical beast,
and there won’t be a problem.
So have there been
any changes on your side?
Colt: Well, there is something
that’s been bothering me.
- Morel: Oh, yeah? What’s that?
- ( Object shatters )
Colt: It’s just reina.
Girl: You’re wrong, you dummy!
I told you!
Colt: She keeps saying
her name’s not reina.
Morel: Okay, what is it, then?
Girl: For the last time, my name
is not reina, all right?!
So stop it! Don’t call me that!
My name is kite!
♪
Morel: Gon!
( Groans ) Killua!
♪
( Knuckle gasps )
Doctor, how is he?
How’s gon?
Doctor: His condition
is still critical.
Normally, I would recommend
that he be transported
to a specialist,
but until he can be
taken off life support,
it’s too risky.
I’ve seen a lot in my time,
but a 12-year-old boy
transformed like that
in one day...
Knov: I see.
Then we’ll just have
to bring the specialist to us.
Considering his heroism,
he deserves at least that much.
I’ll cover all of the expenses.
If necessary, we’ll rebuild
the whole hospital.
But know this.
We are never
going to let gon die.
( Ventilator hissing )
Killua: In the end,
you took care of it
all by yourself.
♪
Gon: I promise.
I’ll take him on myself.
Killua: I get it.
Kite saved your life,
and it wasn’t my fight.
But still...
I’d wish you’d said,
"let’s get him together."
Gon: Let’s go.
Killua: When you said that,
were you ordering me
as your teammate,
or were you telling me
as your friend?
I know. I’m just sulking.
Every time, it’s the same.
You keep running ahead,
while I stay behind
and clean up after you.
It’s the same as always.
And i’ll do it again.
But this time,
I won’t let you off the hook.
You’d better apologize.
I’m going to make you better.
You hear me?
I swear!
I’m gonna make you apologize!
Knov: Killua.
Gon needs lots of help,
so i’m assembling specialists.
I’ll use hide-and-seek
to transport the equipment
and the medical staff,
so I need to fly out now.
Want to come along?
Killua: No. I’ll pass.
( Knov sighs ) I understand.
It’s important for someone
to stay by his side
and keep talking to him.
Killua: I’m going to save gon.
Knov: Wha...
Killua: Go ahead
and get the doctors,
’cause he’s gonna need ’em...
Right up until I get back.
Knov: Killua?
Killua: If anybody’s
gonna save gon, it’s me.
( Static crackling )
( Tape rattles )
Netero: Uh, my name is netero.
I am resigning as chairman,
so please take care.
( Clears throat )
The next chairman will be chosen
by special election,
and I am setting the condition
that all hunters
must cast a vote.
If you don’t reach a 95% quorum,
then call for a revote.
All the other details, such
as the exact date and method,
can be determined
by the zodiacs.
I’d say it’s
a level-d difficulty.
All right, I leave it to you.
I wish you well.
Narrator: In response
to netero’s prerecorded message,
the zodiacs, the leaders
of the hunter association,
assembled at headquarters
that very day.
♪
( Singing in Japanese )