Illumi: You removed the needle,
didn’t you?
Killua: I did.
I feel better now.
Illumi: Then I won’t have
to hold back when I kill you.
Killua: Kill me? Seriously?
( Illumi chuckles )
You can’t kill family members
during an intra-mission.
I’d never kill family.
♪
Silva: It is not
a member of the family.
( Teeth grind )
( Nen whooshes )
Killua: They’re just
a bunch of bullies,
every last one of them.
( Cell phone cracks )
Then bring it on.
I’ll beat you at your own game.
♪
( Singing in Japanese )
♪ You can smile again
( singing in Japanese )
♪ You can fly away
( Wind blowing )
( Running footsteps crunching )
♪
Narrator:
In an attempt to save gon,
killua is heading
for the city with alluka.
Meanwhile, hisoka,
who is currently working
with illumi to kill alluka,
confronts gotoh,
as well as the other butlers
who were escorting them.
Hisoka: A power that lets you
rapidly fire coins
more powerful than bullets...
Powerful enough to explain
why you would send
your subordinates away.
Gotoh: My coins
pack enough power
that you can’t escape unscathed
if they hit.
It must have something to do
with his ability.
( Coins jingling )
Gotoh: Hmm.
Hisoka: I see you’re confused.
My aura has qualities
of both gum and rubber.
Gotoh: Showing
your hand already?
You may regret that,
cheap conjurer.
Hisoka: What’s the point
in hiding things from the dead?
It doesn’t matter
if you know my ability.
( Gotoh grunts ) I think not!
♪
Hisoka: Now catch.
I can’t tell if i’m just
getting used to your attacks
or they’re getting much slower.
Gotoh: Yeah.
They’re a lot slower.
Hisoka: Hmm?
Gotoh: To make them spin,
I diverted a bit of my power.
♪
You’d better disengage soon,
or your own aura
will strangle you.
Or do you want
to be riddled with holes?
Pick your poison!
Hisoka: Bungee gum, disengage.
Gotoh: He dodged it
from that position?
( Grunts )
He’s too fast for me to follow.
Hisoka: You see, I sent
my gum out with the first card.
That way, as soon as I removed
the gum from my feet,
it would be ready
to activate at any time.
And now a lethal pop quiz
from the grim reaper.
I took 22 coins
from your attack.
So the question is...
How many of them
will I return to you?
Gotoh: He’s going
to use his rubber
to send the coins
flying back at me?
Hisoka: You’ll have to find out
the answer for yourself.
Gum release.
♪
Gotoh: Don’t underestimate me.
Even if the answer
is greater than 22,
i’ll shoot them all down!
( Yells )
Hisoka: The answer is
enough to kill you.
Waah, waah.
A grim reaper’s pop quiz
doesn’t need an answer.
Mmm.
( Chuckles )
( Wind blowing )
( Brush rustling )
Killua: 40 kilometers
until we reach the next town.
I can make it.
Hey, alluka, you’re gonna feel
a little zap again, all right?
Alluka: Mm-hmm. It’s fine.
Killua: Godspeed!
Tsubone: Hmm?
Killua: Lightning speed!
Tsubone: Oh.
Very impressive.
If he runs at that speed
on pavement,
I won’t be able to catch up
on my own. That’s for sure.
( Dials cell phone )
( Phone line rings )
( Click )
Amane, it’s tsubone.
Master killua
is headed for parasta.
I need you to follow the road.
Amane: Canary, come with me.
( Canary grunts )
Amane: On grandmother’s bike,
two will be faster.
( Canary gasps )
( Running footsteps )
( Gasps )
( Engine revs )
What is this?
Amane: My grandmother.
Hang on as tight as you can.
We’ll be using our aura as fuel.
It will exhaust you much faster
than running, so be prepared.
♪
Tsubone: Let’s go.
( Tires squeal)
♪
( Canary groans )
( Tires squealing )
Amane: Hey, I found them!
Killua: Really?
I know i’m carrying alluka,
but lightning speed
is at full power!
( Tires squealing )
Killua: All right.
Good luck following me this way!
Amane: What do we do now?
Tsubone: We’ll have
to head him off.
Amane: Where?
Tsubone:
At master killua’s speed,
it’ll take him less than
ten minutes to reach parasta.
It would take master illumi
over 20 minutes by car.
What will he do
with his ten-minute lead?
Amane: A disguise?
Tsubone: Wrong. Cute answer,
though not entirely impossible,
I suppose.
What’s the first thing
master killua will do
after he loses us?
Amane: Contact his friends.
Tsubone: Bingo! And how
can he contact his friends
without us finding out?
Any ideas?
Amane: Well, he’ll need to check
for any tracing
or listening devices
and probably use
someone else’s phone, I guess.
Tsubone: No, no.
That’s just common sense.
Think about what matters
in this situation.
We may know
where master killua is,
but if we can’t get near him,
we won’t have any way
of knowing what he’s up to.
So where is he going?
( Amane grunts )
( Canary gasps )
Tsubone: You’ve figured it out?
Well, let’s go, then!
( Rotors whirring )
( Killua panting )
Amane: We’ve been waiting.
Killua: Damn it.
You guys are really good.
Amane: We already have
an airship prepared for you.
Killua: Oh, really. How many?
Amane: What?
Killua: Sounds like
you only have one.
Are you serious?
Give me a break!
We’ll never
lose illumi like that!
We need at least six airships
going different ways!
You guys better split up
and go make the arrangements!
Canary: This airship
will take us
straight to our destination.
Amane: Fine.
Canary: We’ll have to pay
for two tickets,
or else they’ll
figure out it’s unmanned.
Amane: I know that!
Do I look like an idiot?
Canary: Um, I don’t know
how to read this.
Amane: Just ask the clerk.
Canary: But what names
do you think
we should put
the tickets under?
Amane: Oh, come on!
Can’t you think for yourself?!
( Gasps )
Where’s master killua?
Oh, god damn it!
( Gasps ) Hold on!
You were pestering me
as a distraction
so they could escape,
weren’t you?
Canary: Whatever do you mean?
( Amane groans )
We have to go after them!
- Canary: That’s on you.
- Amane: Huh?!
Canary: As soon as i’ve
dispatched the other flights,
i’ll ride on one of them.
If you follow them
using ground transport,
- be sure you aren’t followed.
- Amane: Wait. What?
If you follow them by air,
it will be a lot more obvious!
Are you out
of your flipping mind?!
Canary: That wasn’t my plan.
I’ll just be a decoy.
And since i’m going
to meet up with gotoh,
it’ll be a whole lot easier
to move there by airship.
Hmm.
( Amane groans )
What is it?
Canary: You’re cute
when you let loose a little.
( Amane gasps )
Canary: I’m sure master killua
will like you more that way.
Amane: Hey! You’re not
making fun of me, are you?
Canary: No, not at all.
I really mean it.
( Amane groans )
( Rotors whirring )
( Cell phone ringing )
Canary: Gotoh...
- ( Rotors whirring )
- ( Phone line ringing )
- ( Click )
- Killua: Hello? It’s killua.
Morel: Hey, what’s going on?
I was getting worried.
I can’t get in touch
with Mr. Gotoh.
Killua: Got it.
I’ll try giving him a call.
Morel: Wait. So he wants
to kill your brother?
Killua: Yeah.
If we’re gonna heal gon,
alluka’s the only one
who can do it.
Problem is,
illumi wants to kill alluka.
Thing is, if my wish is granted,
it may end up wiping out
my entire family.
Hisoka: We’re too late.
I still don’t see why
we don’t wait for them
around the hospital.
Illumi: As we draw
near the hospital,
our chance for failure
starts to increase.
All of killua’s friends
will be swarming the area.
And if we just
hang around waiting,
they’ll realize
something’s not right.
♪
Illumi: Eight. We’re going
to need more people.
Hisoka: Are you
calling in friends?
To be honest with you,
i’m pretty shy.
Illumi: No.
I don’t have any of those.
What a waste, but i’ll
have to use my needles.
Hisoka: Hmm?
Ohh.
Now, that is
an excellent aura.
( Sighs )
Illumi: If I
stick them in someone,
they’ll work for me
until they die.
Or, rather, they’ll drop dead
from working too hard.
Morel: Grant a wish?
Wow. That’s a dangerous ability.
Imagine what would happen
if the wrong hands got to it.
Killua: Illumi will probably
follow the airships by ground.
My butlers
have dispatched seven decoys.
I know my brother doesn’t have
any allies for this,
so he’ll use the needle people.
Morel: What are those?
Killua: He uses
special nen needles
to create soldiers to do
his bidding until they die.
Illumi’s powerful aura enters
the victims through the needles.
( All groaning )
Killua: So the moment
they’re pierced,
they turn into puppets,
and they’ll do
whatever he wants them to.
( Puppets moaning )
Killua: I need you
to call on the hunters.
Grab the needle people.
Can you do that?
If we have proof
he’s harmed people,
all innocent civilians,
beyond recovery...
They can arrest him even if
he’s a pro hunter, right?
( Morel gasps )
Narrator: Killua sought
to confirm this theory
because of a statement made
in a particular section
of the hunter bylaws.
Article four of the hunter
bylaws states,
"hunters shall not
target other hunters.
"The one exception shall be that
if the hunter to be targeted
has committed heinous crimes."
Killua: I believe
that some of the candidates
had eyes on the bylaws.
They were talking
about revising them,
as well as the hunter exam.
If we catch illumi,
we both know how that will go.
It’ll just drum up
sympathy for their cause.
( Morel gasps ) Wait! You sure?
You would be sellin’ out
your own brother.
Killua: He’s trying
to hurt alluka,
and that’s something
I can’t forgive,
not my big brother, not anyone.
That’s my line in the sand.
Cross it, and i’ll crush you.
( Morel gasps )
I understand.
Teradein and bushidora
will probably agree to help.
There should be plenty of
hunters who’ll lend us a hand.
Since you’ve decided
to come to the city
where the hunter association
headquarters is located,
you’ll be right under our noses.
That said, i’ll make sure
that everyone knows
how dangerous our opponent is.
We won’t touch illumi.
We’ll just capture
all of the needle people.
Killua: Yeah. Sounds good.
Man: All right.
I’ve accessed
parasta airport’s flight logs.
There are six airships that
will be landing in this area
within 20 to 30 kilometers
of the hospital.
As for killua and his butlers,
we’re not sure
where they’ll land,
and illumi can’t pursue
what he can’t see.
He and the needle people
will try to stay
within visual range
of the airships
as they follow on the ground.
Man 2: They’ll be vulnerable
to attack at a number of points
before they reach swardani city,
where the hospital is,
so of course
we need to send hunters
to each of those checkpoints.
Man 1: We have
one main priority,
the capture
of the needle people.
Teradein:
We can confirm needles later!
Just capture anyone
approaching the airship!
Now get moving!
Illumi: Go.
♪
Illumi: Can you start hunting
the fakes for me, hisoka?
Hisoka: Okay.
This is gonna get busy.
Bushidora: Not surprised.
I always knew that article four
was fundamentally flawed.
We can’t just wait for a crisis
like this to appear,
not when the hunter
association’s honor
is at stake.
Teradein:
The problem is that the exam
needs to be more selective.
If good behavior was
a prerequisite for joining,
well, we wouldn’t
have this problem.
Loupe: The time has come
for we three members
of the anti-netero faction
to have more pull
in the association.
Teradein: Hello, everyone.
Today I, teradein,
joined forces with loupe,
as well as our associate,
bushidora.
Now, we three
are most commonly known
as the anti-netero faction,
but that’s not a name
of our choosing.
The hunter souls deep within us
were inherited
from the former chairman,
as so many of yours were.
Of that, I can assure you.
And so, in order
to carry out his will,
we seek to reinstate
the highly versatile team
to which
the former chairman belonged.
As many of you may recall,
this elite group was known as...
The legendary
pure paladin squad.
Bushidora:
Teradein, the leader,
loupe, his deputy,
and finally I,
bushidora ambitious, am honored
to serve as the captain
of the new pure paladins.
To express our solidarity during
this critical election process,
we have only one request,
and that is that all your votes
be cast for our leader.
If you agree with our message,
give your support
to our ally, teradein,
and together we’ll know
the sweet taste of victory.
Loupe: Also, as we continue to
address our faction’s message,
we would be remiss
not to mention
that we have recently
received information
from a very reliable
and trustworthy source
which states
that multiple parties
have found a certain hunter
guilty of many egregious crimes.
Teradein:
I would like to announce
that we are currently
pursuing this hunter.
Ladies and gentlemen,
let us come together
to start to rebuild
the hunter association
with wisdom and integrity
as our tools.
♪
Narrator: The zoldycks’ conflict
over alluka intensifies,
so much so that it reaches
beyond the scope of one family
and seeps into the hunter
association elections.
♪
( Singing in Japanese )