♪
Gon: Why?!
( Aura exploding )
Must be real nice for you.
You can stay calm...
Because it’s not your fight.
( Killua gasps )
Narrator: Gon’s cry led meleoron
directly to the two boys.
♪
( Singing in Japanese )
Zeno: I’m going
to have to refuse.
I’m just not in the mood.
Cheetu: Aw, come on.
Don’t be like that.
Just think of it as bad luck
that I was even
able to find you.
I wanna test my new ability,
and you’re right here.
( Zeno sighs )
Cheetu: Oh, man, that hurts.
There’s no need
to look at me like that.
I feel the same as you.
I’d rather be out here
fighting someone else, too.
The sunglasses guy
with the really big pipe,
you tag along with him,
don’t you?
Zeno: You want him?
Then I suggest that you
go out and look for him.
Cheetu: I know where he is,
but I can’t get to him.
He controls smoke,
and he’s hidden himself
behind a smoke screen,
and no matter how hard I try,
I just can’t get through.
I scaled the roof to see
if I could get in from above...
Huh?
And I just so happened
to spot you.
Zeno: Ah, so i’m
just a little warm-up
before you reach
your real target.
Is that about right?
Cheetu: We have a winner!
( Wind blowing )
Zeno: I’m feeling
very tired today.
Cheetu: Huh?
Zeno: Let me have your ear
for a moment.
For the very first time since
taking over the family business,
I may have accidentally killed
someone who wasn’t my target.
Cheetu: Hey, come on!
My technique is incredible,
so just try not to be
too shocked when you see it.
Well, there’ll be lots of time
for you to be shocked
when we’re through.
( Zeno sighs )
Just how self-centered
can you be?
It doesn’t look
like i’ll be able
to persuade you to let me go.
Cheetu: You win again!
Huh?
Zeno: You know, if I were you,
I would keep a keen eye
on my back.
( Cheetu laughs )
Yeah, nice try.
I’m not falling for that.
See? I learned something
from one of your buddies,
never take your eyes off--
Zeno: Well...
Looking wouldn’t have helped you
all that much anyway.
Silva: Would you have
preferred I spared him?
Zeno: Hmm? Nah, not really.
Silva: How’s killua doing?
Zeno: Hmm? He’s matured.
And I have reason to believe
he’s removed illumi’s needle.
Silva: I see.
Zeno: Oh, I almost forgot.
I had quite
the bizarre experience.
You see, it felt as if
time was being condensed.
Silva: I should
take your stories
with a grain of salt, dad.
♪
Killua: Okay. You and I
should be safe here.
What’s the update?
( Meleoron exhales )
God’s accomplice, deactivate.
Shoot is completely
out of commission,
and knuckle is trying
to fight youpi all by himself.
You gotta help.
Knuckle is gonna keep
running around, avoiding youpi
to try and buy us more time.
He’s out of his mind.
Killua: Okay.
What’s the maximum time
you can use god’s accomplice?
Meleoron: The first time,
I was so nervous,
that I tapped out
after just ten seconds,
but i’ve calmed down now.
I could go a full minute
if I don’t have to move.
Killua: That’s plenty,
’cause all i’m gonna need
is one shot.
Narrator:
Approximately three minutes
before killua
raised his finger...
Knuckle was in the air.
He thought his best asset
was his ability
to make a quick getaway.
Knuckle: Huh?
( Gasping )
( Sirens blaring )
Narrator: Once,
he punched out a cop
to help his friend escape
and spent all day and night
running around,
eluding four patrol cars
and dozens of police.
And this was the day
he graduated from grade school.
He was never caught.
( Knuckle yelling )
Narrator: His ability
to maintain his stamina
while running at top speed
far outshines that of a cheetah.
Knuckle revealed his presence
to save shoot
and focused his energy
on keeping his enemy distracted.
For the most part,
it was the right choice.
Knuckle: Eh?
♪
He stopped chasing me?
Narrator: If he erred,
it was in his assessment
of youpi’s perceptions.
Knuckle: Damn.
Shoot’s in trouble.
Knuckle: For both
shoot and knuckle,
youpi was
a high-priority target,
but the reverse
was not true for youpi.
As a royal guard,
his mission
was protecting the king.
His focus was on keeping enemies
far away from him.
Youpi could only assume
that the king
was still in the throne room.
Since he had been assigned to
keep watch over the staircase,
he also assumed that two other
royal guards, pitou and pouf,
were currently
protecting the king.
This meant
that his main priority
was to keep enemies
from getting anywhere
close to the throne room.
Since he didn’t know
how many enemies there were,
the nature
of his opponent’s ability
was of a lower priority,
as were enemies
who were escaping or dying.
They did not warrant
his concern.
Menthuthuyoupi:
Pitou, where are you?!
( Knuckle gasps )
( Gasps )
( Shoot groaning )
Knuckle: Shoot!
Narrator: Shoot was still alive.
Knuckle: Shoot, I...
( Chorus vocalizing )
( Gasps )
Narrator: Given their positions,
it was abundantly clear
that youpi had seen shoot
when he passed by.
( Shoot groaning )
Knuckle: This guy
doesn’t even think that...
We’re worth the effort
to try and kill off.
Narrator: It was true.
Youpi didn’t care
whether shoot lived or died.
This was an unprecedented insult
to them both,
who had risked everything
in this battle.
( Knuckle growls )
Are shoot and I
nothing more than gnats to him?
Is that how it is?!
Fine, then, but you’re
gonna regret it later,
because us gnats
are gonna make you go bankrupt
in about ten minutes!
Menthuthuyoupi:
Hey, pouf and pitou!
Hey, are you there?!
Knuckle: The boss used
smoky jail on the throne room.
That must mean that
he and pouf are in there alone,
so the king is somewhere else.
Menthuthuyoupi: Say something!
Can’t you hear me?! Hey!
( Knuckle laughs )
You moron.
Go defend the empty room.
I’ll take shoot,
and we’ll both watch
from a safe distance.
( Shoot groans )
Damn it.
( Knuckle gasps )
♪
Narrator: By the time
knuckle realized
that he had made an error,
he had already
made another one.
Knuckle: Youpi’s eyes
had met with shoot’s.
Shoot must have
been prepared to die
right then and there.
We knew death was
a possibility going in.
Shoot was right there,
and youpi ignored him.
Narrator: When knuckle
imagined the expression
on youpi’s face as he
glanced at the bloodied shoot
and walked right past him
on his way to the third floor,
he realized that he had
made yet another error.
Shoot: Damn it.
Damn it.
Knuckle: How can I
ignore the fact
that my friend was insulted?
And why? For what reason?
For the world? For humanity?
And what am I supposed to do
if our mission succeeds?
Just shake shoot’s hand
and say, "we did it"?
Pat each other on the back
and laugh?
Do we just
let this insult slide?
There’s no way in hell!
This is so unreal.
( Shoot groans )
Hey. What...The hell?
Knuckle: Oh. Sorry.
And speaking of sorry,
i’m gonna need you to wait here
a little bit longer.
I haven’t punched that bastard
in the face yet,
and i’ve gotta correct that.
I promise that when I do,
I swear i’ll lay one in
from you, too.
Shoot: I know
that my job right now
should be to try
and stop knuckle.
"Are you crazy?" "Don’t go."
"Just keep your mouth shut,
and buy more time."
That’s what I should
be saying to him.
Please, knuckle! I beg you!
That son of a bitch,
the way he looked at me,
it was like--it was like...
I was nothing more than trash!
( Crying )
When you find him...
Punch that bastard for me!
Knuckle: Yeah. I got this.
Sorry, master,
but the thing is,
we’re both idiots.
Some things are more important
than saving the world.
Narrator: A brand-new error,
the significance
of something important.
♪
( Menthuthuyoupi grunts )
My attacks don’t have
any effect on this smoke.
Sire!
Pitou, pouf, are you there?!
Answer me!
Morel: Is that youpi?
No way. Did shoot
and knuckle get killed?
I hope the old man’s
doing okay.
Pouf’s not responding.
I wonder why.
Something’s wrong.
How in the hell can he stay
inside his cocoon for so long?
You would think
that he would be rushing
to be back
by the king’s side right now.
We thought we knew
what we were dealing with,
but these royal guards,
did we miscalculate?
I thought our plan
was actually working.
Could I be wrong?
( Grunts ) No second-guessing.
I’m here
to carry out my mission.
Shaiapouf: Suspicion,
anxiety, impatience...
Despite these emotions,
the ratio of his conviction
remains unchanged.
Just as I would expect
from a strong warrior.
I’m impressed.
However, that constraint
will be what inhibits
your decision making.
Menthuthuyoupi: Damn it.
Why the hell
is pitou’s en gone?
Have the king, pitou,
and pouf all vanished?
Did they really decide
to leave me behind?
What happened? What’s going on?
A.p.r.: It is time.
You have accrued interest.
Menthuthuyoupi: Shut up!
♪
The fuzz on my shoulder
won’t go away,
and this stupid thing
keeps counting up.
I’ve gotta find the king fast.
Damn, I should have killed
the gnat downstairs.
That might have
gotten rid of this fuzz.
But right now,
I have to find the king.
What the hell is going on?
It’s pissing me off!
Huh?
Knuckle: Hey.
( Joints pop )
Menthuthuyoupi:
Okay, i’ve had enough!
What is it with you guys?!
Narrator: And as he yelled,
youpi changed form.
It was drastic enough to make
knuckle instantly turn to flee,
even though, moments ago, he’d
been ready to accept the worst.
This was the embodiment
of pure evil,
and clearly it sought
only total destruction.
( Menthuthuyoupi roars )
♪
( Shoot groans )
Knuckle: Just hang on.
Shoot: Did you get him?
Knuckle: Huh?!
Shoot: Did you hit him for me?
Knuckle: No, not yet, damn it.
I promise you
i’m going to, though,
but I can’t let you die
before that happens. Let’s go!
( Explosion booming )
Narrator: Being under
extreme mental stress
for the first time in his life,
youpi became aware
that the true nature
of his ability
was in truth not at all
useful for guard duty.
Rather, he began
to feel his entire body,
as well as his aura,
become engorged
with his furious rage.
The destruction
that was unleashed
was accompanied
by intense pleasure.
Then, as he rapidly deflated,
he was overcome
by a sense of great loss.
Having had more experience,
knuckle instantly understood
what had happened to youpi.
Knuckle: We can win.
That was a powerful blast.
I doubt it’ll be easy
to goad him into doing that
on purpose
and still make it out unharmed.
It’s high-risk--
no doubt about it--
but it’s an even higher return.
I’ll make him mad
so he blows up.
I need to get a strike in,
and that’ll create
the perfect opportunity,
and the aura consumed
in the explosion
will reduce the time
that’s required
for him to go bankrupt.
Narrator: The plan knuckle
instantly envisioned
was close to perfect
for defeating youpi.
But in the moment
after the blast,
youpi proved his worth.
There, standing in the middle
of the gaping chasm
between lingering pleasure
and numbing despair,
youpi was trying
desperately to figure out
how to utilize
this self-indulgent ability
in a way that would
better benefit the king.
Menthuthuyoupi: Selflessness.
Narrator:
The instincts of an ant
and his nature as a magical
beast functioned calmly
even after discovering
his explosive emotions.
Menthuthuyoupi:
The best way I can think of
to serve the king
is to control this fury
without being consumed
by emotion.
In other words, I need to use it
to destroy these pests.
Narrator: Youpi was now armed
with both passion
and presence of mind,
which meant that, for knuckle,
the risks were incredibly high.
Three minutes have passed
since the mission began.
♪
Everyone’s motives
were beginning to merge.
( Singing in Japanese )