♪
Razor: Here I come,
gon.
( Gon gasps )
( Growls )
Bring it!
( Killua gasps )
Gon: Ko!
( Groaning )
Killua: Gon!
Bisky: Are you okay?!
Gon: Yeah, i’m okay,
guys, really.
Killua: Yeah, right!
Gon: I used ko
to guard my arms and head,
but my legs
just couldn’t brace hard enough.
But next time,
i’m gonna catch it for sure.
♪
( Singing in Japanese )
Narrator: An intense
dodge ball match has begun.
Gon was injured
by razor’s mighty throw,
but even
through the extreme pain,
his eyes burn with fire.
Number zero: Estimating
the ball’s drop point.
The game will continue!
Team gon has possession,
and since the ceiling
is considered an extension
of the floor, gon is out.
Gon: Okay. I’m gonna use "back."
- Bisky: You can’t be serious!
- Gon: I’m doing it.
Killua: He won’t listen,
so don’t even try it.
Bisky: Fine. Have it your way.
However, I forbid you
to use "back"
until we’re down
to two inside players. Got it?
Number zero:
Now let’s get started.
Killua: Get patched up, gon.
Hey, it’s not against the rules
to keep passing the ball
like this, is it?
Number zero: No, you’re fine.
Gon: ’kay. I’m better now.
Killua: Hey!
Goreinu: Just so you know,
i’m the type to hold a grudge.
It’s time for payback, razor.
( Razor chuckles )
Goreinu: Take this.
Black goreinu!
Razor: The black one
switches with others?
Damn, you really got me good.
That’s what you get.
You mess with me,
and i’ll take you out.
Killua: Razor will use "back"
to return to play anyway.
At least we made him
use it up early.
Plus, it’ll be our ball.
Goreinu: Huh?
♪
What in the hell?
( Groans )
- ( Bisky gasps )
- Killua: Goreinu!
Razor: Now, that’s
one interesting ability.
Nurture it well, okay?
Bisky: Hey,
hold on just a second.
What the heck was that?
Razor: Hmm?
There’s no rule against passing
the ball to an opponent.
( Bisky groans )
And as you’ve probably noticed,
you’re welcome
to hit people in the face here.
That means that his attack
was also legal.
If the ball had actually touched
the floor, i’d be out now.
Once he’s unconscious,
the nen beast disappears.
His ability requires
his direct control.
The black gorilla
may begin inside the court,
but that’s assuming goreinu
ever regains consciousness,
which something tells me
isn’t likely.
Number zero: If the in-court
players are reduced to zero
before goreinu wakes up,
the match will be over.
Kess: There’s no way.
He’s out cold.
Rodriot: He might wake up.
He might even wake up
before we lose,
but in the condition
that he’s in,
he won’t be able to conjure
his nen beast.
Inside the court,
it’s three-on-three...
But we’re seriously outmatched.
That’s obvious.
Half our players are gone,
and we’ve only got one hurt kid
on the outside.
Our opponents have
a solid outside team,
so they can attack
from anywhere.
Razor’s still inside
without having to use "back,"
and the ball rebounded
to our opponents.
We’re at a clear disadvantage.
Razor: All right, well...
Tell me, who wants to be next?!
Killua: Me?
What do I do?
I can’t catch it.
I’ve gotta dodge.
It turned on a dime.
( Hisoka gasps )
( Gasps )
Killua: Hisoka!
Hisoka: Bungee gum!
♪
( Coos )
Killua: That bastard.
Can’t believe it.
He faked going for me,
but his real goal
was taking out
both bisky and hisoka.
Wait a minute.
What if he was gambling
that i’d dodge
to the left instead?
If i’d done that...
Number zero: Biscuit is out.
Step out of the court.
Rodriot: What happened?
Kess: Didn’t she dodge?
Bisky: I’m out.
Both: What?
Bisky: So that means
that clothing
counts as part of your body?
Number zero: Yes.
( Rodriot sighs )
Kess: I was almost positive
she dodged it.
Rodriot: We’re down to two!
No matter what,
don’t let them get the ball!
Gon: Back.
Number zero: Gon has used back
and may now return to the court.
( Rodriot sighs )
Are you sure we can trust
a little kid with this?
Barry: That one’s
no ordinary little kid.
He’s the only one of us
who’s even tried
to catch razor’s throw.
Bisky: Are you all right?
Gon: Yeah.
Bisky: Now listen
to me carefully.
- Do not overdo it.
- Gon: Yeah.
Bisky: Hmm.
What’s one plus one?
Gon: Yeah.
Bisky: It’s hopeless.
Okay, then! Beat him
even if it kills you!
Gon: Osu.
Killua: You all good?
Gon: Yep.
Hisoka: I learned
something rather interesting.
If the ball travels
outside the court,
it becomes much less powerful.
I only broke two fingers
without ko.
Killua: So as long as we
can avoid razor’s attacks,
we might just be okay.
( Bones pop )
Hisoka: My thoughts exactly.
Gon: But what kind
of victory is that?
( Killua gasps )
Look, don’t be an idiot.
If we can’t win,
no matter what we do,
all of this is pointless!
You better calm down.
You’re being stupid.
- Gon: I thought you’d be mad.
- Killua: You what?!
Gon: If you’d dodged left,
then you could have been killed.
- ( Killua gasps )
- Gon: It’s true.
♪
I’m really pissed off right now,
and i’m not gonna settle
for some cheap win.
I have to completely crush
this guy.
Hisoka: Hmm.
In that case, you must have
some kind of plan in mind.
Gon: Yeah.
I’ve got this.
Killua, stand over there.
Bend your knees,
and hold the ball tight.
Killua: Uh, sure.
I get it.
Now show me rock!
Razor: Hmm?
His aura just spiked.
( Men gasp )
Gon: Jan...
Ken...
Rock!
Now show me rock!
Razor: Hmm?
His aura just spiked.
( Men gasp )
Gon: Jan...
Ken...
Rock!
Razor: Oh.
( All gasp )
( Killua gasps ) Huh?
Number zero: Number 13 is out.
Catching the ball
while your body is touching
outside the court is illegal.
Possession goes to team gon.
- Kess: Oh, wow.
- ( Rodriot laughs )
Barry: Did you guys see that?!
He just sent
the biggest one of ’em flying!
Gon: Damn it.
That one wasn’t
nearly good enough.
Kess: Why does he
look so unhappy?
Rodriot: You’re right.
He looks mad.
( Barry laughs )
That kid has got
real high standards.
Gon: Not yet.
That’s not enough
to beat the real razor.
I need a lot more power.
Killua: You ready?
Let’s do it again.
Hit razor
with everything you’ve got.
( Gon grunts )
♪
I’m gonna need
a whole lot more power
if i’m gonna bring down razor.
( Killua gasps )
( Gon breathing deeply )
Ren.
♪
( Tsezguerra gasps )
His aura’s so immense.
Bisky: I think you picked
the wrong sport.
Nothing in the rules
limits the amount of time
he can take
to build up his power.
Might want
to get out of the way.
Razor: You’re kidding, right?
Gon: Take all the built-up aura,
and focus it into my fist.
Okay, show me rock.
( Grunts )
♪
( Bisky grunts )
( Hisoka sighs )
( Killua gasps )
Gon: Take this, razor.
Jan...
Ken...
Rock!
Killua: Perfect.
He’ll never catch that.
( Razor chuckles )
( Gon gasps )
Killua: He’s bumping it?
( Razor grunting )
Hisoka: He used his own body
to slow its momentum.
Bisky: He’s good.
His timing had to be flawless,
and he deflected
the force so smoothly.
This man is really strong.
( Gon gasps )
That was great.
Razor: The game’s not
all about dodging and catching,
but that advice is a bit
too little too late, i’m afraid.
Kess: I don’t get it.
That ball was as strong as his,
but it--it didn’t
even reach the ceiling.
Rodriot: That was
one hell of a bump
to burn off all that momentum.
Now it’s right above him.
( Razor gasps )
Hisoka: Bungee gum.
Aww, that’s too bad.
You’re actually supposed
to catch it, you know.
Number zero: As per
the cushion rule, razor is out.
Step outside.
( Razor grunts )
I call "back."
Number zero:
Razor has used "back."
He will remain inside the court,
and play will resume.
Kess: Both teams
have used "back,"
and it’s three-on-two.
Rodriot: Yeah, looks like
the tables have turned.
Tsezguerra: You really think so?
Men: Eh?
Tsezguerra:
From where i’m sitting,
our team is the one
on the ropes.
Hisoka probably isn’t
in any shape to throw.
I’d be surprised
if he could even
hold the ball
with his right hand.
Gon’s attacks used
a huge amount of aura.
That takes its toll.
He should feel completely
drained right about now.
( Gon grunts )
Tsezguerra: Can he muster
another attack that powerful?
It’s highly unlikely.
Barry: That means killua’s
the only uninjured one inside?
Tsezguerra: Quite the opposite.
( Men gasp )
Tsezguerra: I would venture
that of the three,
he’s probably
the most gravely injured.
Rodriot: What do you mean?
( Gon exhales )
Killua: Are you
doin’ okay there, gon?
Gon: Yeah, but I think
the next one will be the last,
so i’ll give it
everything i’ve got.
Killua: All right.
Just make it good.
One more. I can take it.
I’ve just gotta hold out.
Tsezguerra: When gon struck
the ball, I noticed that killua
barely used any protective nen
on his hands.
Kess: That’s crazy.
That launch was intense.
He was like a damn Cannon.
Tsezguerra: Correct,
and essentially
killua used his bare hands
to form that cannon’s barrel.
But with
the right amount of nen,
if he’d used
just enough to protect them,
his aura would have become
a barrier against gon’s punch,
significantly reducing
the amount of power to the ball.
In order to keep himself from
weakening the ball’s velocity,
killua used hardly
any aura on his hands,
sacrificing them
in the process.
That tells me that as bad
as hisoka’s right hand
might be at the moment,
killua’s hands must be
in much worse condition.
Damn.
I feel like such a fool.
Why am I not
up there with them?
I know the technique, and I can
do it much faster than killua.
In the moment
before gon touches the ball,
I could swiftly switch
my aura to my hands,
a near-instant transfer.
Wait.
Timeout. Hey, ref, question.
Number zero: Yes, what is it?
Tsezguerra: I was just wondering
if the players
inside of the court
can choose to move
to the outside.
Number zero: Well,
that doesn’t violate any rules,
but be aware
that you can’t return inside.
Tsezguerra: All right.
Come here!
Gon, if you just step outside
of the court before you strike,
I can hold the ball for you.
Killua’s hands must be
totally ravaged by now.
I sincerely doubt
that he’s in any condition
to hold the ball
or anything else.
♪
I know a way that’ll allow me
to protect my hands
with a lightning-fast
coating of aura.
I can hold the ball while you
take out razor from here.
It’s the only way
that we can win this.
Killua: We can’t do that.
Tsezguerra: But why not?
What’s the problem with that?
Killua: It feels like a cop-out.
Tsezguerra: You’re kidding!
This is not the time
to be thinking like that!
( Groans, coughs )
Killua: Hey,
don’t overdo it, old man.
You took a hit.
You’re only gonna
make it feel worse.
I’m doin’ fine.
I’m not hurt nearly as bad
as you might think.
Tsezguerra: Okay, then.
Show me your hands.
Killua: I said i’m fine.
( Killua winces )
( Tsezguerra gasps )
♪
Like I thought.
I’ll bet you he can’t feel
anything but pain.
Killua: I can do this!
I can take one more, okay?
Gon, I know I can do it.
Tsezguerra: Impossible.
I’m right.
Please help me convince him.
Gon: I--i already knew...
That killua’s hands were hurt.
I’m sorry, Mr. Tsezguerra,
but I won’t move
out of the court.
Tsezguerra: Eh?
Gon: I need him
to hold the ball for me.
I can’t do this without killua.
( Killua gasps )
Gon: If biscuit
or hisoka held it,
I probably couldn’t use
my full strength.
There’s only one reason
I can focus everything i’ve got
on hitting the ball.
It’s because I know
killua’s the one holding it.
Killua: There it is, old man.
Do you get it now?
Why don’t you go get some rest?
Tsezguerra: I understand.
Good luck.
♪
Bisky: The ball,
give it here, hisoka.
Number zero: We will
now resume the match.
Bisky: Now,
to be perfectly honest,
i’m not very good at throwing!
Looks to me like we’re even.
Kess: Brilliant!
The way she hit him
is rebounding the ball to us.
( Groans )
Number zero: Number two is out.
Hisoka: And that means
we’re down to...
Gon: Razor himself.
Killua: Gon, first we need
to get the ball back from razor.
Gon: No sweat.
Oh.
One sec.
Hisoka: I see. Sounds like fun.
Killua: Yeah. I’m just
not convinced it’s gonna work.
Hisoka: Maybe not,
but i’d certainly
love to try either way.
Gon: Let’s give it
a shot, killua.
Killua: Okay.
Hisoka: I believe
that settles it. ( Giggles )
Killua: Man...
You always come up with
the craziest ideas, don’t you?
( Gon laughs )
I’m counting on you.
Number zero: We will
now resume the match!
♪
Narrator: Gon and killua share
a powerful bond of mutual trust.
Their friendship is strong,
but when hisoka
is added to the equation,
there’s no telling what sort
of secret play will emerge.
( Singing in Japanese )