Neferpitou: It’s neferpitou.
- Rammot: Huh?
- Peggy: Eh?
Neferpitou: That is the name
the queen bestowed upon me.
From now on,
you can call me neferpitou.
♪
( Singing in Japanese )
Peggy: Attention,
squadron leaders and officers.
Attention, squadron leaders
and officers.
Commander neferpitou
will be holding
a conferment ceremony
in hall one,
and of course
you are all invited.
( Rammot chuckles )
( Knuckles crack )
Peggy: A brief moment
of suffering, and in exchange,
you will be rewarded with power
beyond your wildest dreams.
All we ask in return
is that you use this power
in service of the queen.
♪
Kite: They’re still moving
in a straight line,
and that can only mean
that the chimera ant nest
is almost certainly up ahead.
Killua: Man, that’s amazing.
He tracked ’em this whole time
and never lost them once.
Gon: He said that his en
covers a radius of 45 meters.
Killua: I’ve heard that
the ones called nen masters
can handle around 50 meters.
I’m guessing that kite’s
nearly there.
Actually, he’s kept it up
for a whole night,
so he’s probably stronger.
Gon: Stronger
than a master, huh?
♪
He must be the real deal,
I guess.
Killua: Yeah.
He’s the first pro we’ve met,
well, at least like this.
( No audible dialogue )
I mean, tsezguerra was
definitely a pro hunter,
but we really only knew him
as another player in a game.
And bisky was an incredible
hunter, but to us...
Gon: Yeah.
She was our nen master.
Killua: And then
there was the first person
to teach us about nen...
Gon: Master wing,
our nen master and savior.
Killua: And now
that I think about it,
we always meet people
when we need them the most.
It’s them,
all these people we’ve met,
who have made us stronger.
Gon: I guess razor counts,
too, huh?
Killua: Yeah.
It’s pretty obvious to me
that ging really did create
"greed island" to train you,
and then once you
finished beating the game,
he led you to kite.
Gon: Yeah!
♪
Killua: I don’t know
if ging could have predicted
what was gonna happen
when we met kite, but still...
Kite had already
earned his respect,
so he had to have known
that you would like him, too,
and he definitely knew
you’d follow him.
That much, i’m sure of.
Gon: If he wants us
to travel with kite,
then that means
he’ll make us stronger.
Killua: You might be right,
but this is a pretty brutal
place for training.
Kite: And that is
exactly the reason
why I keep asking you
if your resolve is firm.
( Both gasp )
Kite: I agree that,
like you mentioned,
ging probably did have
certain expectations
when he sent you here
to meet with me.
That being said,
I have no intention
of training the two of you
during this journey.
We just don’t have
that kind of time.
♪
I only brought you along,
because I thought
you might be useful.
From here on, it all comes down
to your resolve.
If it’s strong,
you’ll develop your nen
and improve through combat.
If it’s weak, the ants
will eat you, and you will die.
( Both grunt )
Kite: But that’s not
a luxury we can afford.
We’re professional hunters,
after all,
and as you’re aware,
those who call themselves
hunters must get their prey.
( Both gasp )
Kite: For those
of our profession,
that’s the first commandment.
We stay on the hunt,
no matter what.
A hunt involves both
the hunter and the hunted.
It’s a battle of resolve.
Emerging victorious
from a battle of resolve
is what makes a hunt successful.
The loser must follow
the winner’s rules and customs,
and this often means
the loser’s death.
Gon: Yeah. Okay.
Kite: If that result
isn’t desirable, then win.
Improving your nen
is important, sure,
but to be a successful hunter,
you must understand your enemy
as well as yourself.
Gon: Wait. I get it!
That must be why you hit me
when I met you
a long time ago, right?
♪
Kite: You imbecile!
Don’t you know better
than to enter a snakebeech
forest this time of year?!
- ( Gon gasps )
- Kite: See that?
It’s the territorial Mark of
a foxbear when she’s with a cub!
If you see that Mark,
then you stay away!
Even the animals know that much!
( Gon gasps )
That was the rule of the forest.
It was, wasn’t it?
You were teaching me the rules
in ging’s place.
( Kite gasps )
( Both gasp )
Kite: Oh, that’s right.
I just remembered.
Gon: It’s a hunter’s license.
Killua: But whose?
Kite: It’s ging’s.
Gon: Huh? It’s ging’s?
Kite: Just think back
to my final test.
Remember what it was?
Gon: Mm. You told me
you had to go find ging.
Kite: Well,
before the test even began,
ging handed his license to me.
He told me I was supposed
to use it to find him someday.
♪
I always planned
to return it to him once I did.
Gon: Wait.
He wouldn’t take it back?
Kite: No. I’d actually
forgotten I had it.
( Both groan )
Kite: Gon, you said you were
gonna find ging on your own,
didn’t you?
Gon: Uh...
( Grunts )
Kite: Then you have to do
what you said you would.
And if you don’t mind,
you think you could
return that to him for me?
Gon: Sure,
but before I do that,
I have to finish
this job with you
and get a lot stronger
while we’re at it.
Once i’m done, i’ll find ging
and give this back to him.
You have my word.
Kite: I’m counting on you.
Well, time to get a move on.
We don’t want to lose the trail.
( Rammot yells )
( Chimera ant crashes )
Who’s next?
Neferpitou:
Must be tough being ordinary,
going through all this trouble
just to become powerful.
( Rammot grunts )
( Neferpitou giggles )
Peggy, take care of the rest.
Peggy: Where are you going?
Neferpitou:
To check on something.
I want to see
just how strong I am.
Kite: A monster.
What is this?
I don’t believe it!
Gon: What’s wrong, kite?
Kite: Gon, killua, run.
Both: Huh?
Kite: I said go!
Get out of here right now!
♪
Neferpitou: I found you.
Kite: Get away!
( Both gasp )
( No audio )
( Audio returns )
( Gon shudders )
( Yells )
Kite: Idiot!
Wise decision, killua.
Now take gon,
and get out of here!
( Killua gasps )
( Wind blowing )
( Crazy slots laughs )
You’re in for it now.
You know that?
Better hope for a good number.
( Babbles )
Three!
Neferpitou: So you can
do that stuff, too?
Killua: We were too complacent
and overconfident.
♪
We were both worth less
than a one-armed kite.
That was his assessment.
That’s the reality.
If kite had been alone,
this probably
wouldn’t have happened.
( Gasps )
Damn it. We were fools.
Man: Hey...
Is that...
( Killua panting )
♪
( Cell phone beeping )
( Line ringing )
Spin: What?
You left kite behind?
Why would you do that?!
What happened out there?!
You explain yourself
this instant!
Hey, what the hell
do you think you’re doing?!
Mon: Mm. I understand.
Just wait there
for the time being.
We’re all headed your way
right now, so it won’t be long.
And we’re
bringing reinforcements.
Killua: Huh?
( Sighs )
( Gasps )
♪
Chairman netero.
Hunter: What the hell is this?
They’re just kids.
You got burned real bad,
because you thought
this was gonna be a game.
Just hurry on home
before it’s too late.
Hunter #2: Stop it, Mr. Morel.
That isn’t very nice.
( Morel growls )
Hunter #2: As you said yourself,
they are only children.
( Netero chuckles )
You certainly seem to be
down in the dumps.
So was your adversary
that formidable?
( Killua gasps )
One of them could use nen.
Of all the aura
i’ve encountered,
this one was the worst...
Worse than my brother’s...
Or hisoka’s.
Now that i’ve learned nen
myself, I can tell.
You guys are
unbelievably strong...
And still, I don’t think
even you could take him.
( Hunter #2 scoffs )
People overrate things
that they can’t understand,
and that is
a perfectly natural response.
Unfortunately you’re in a state
of extreme panic right now.
We’ll take it from here.
You just go to bed
and get some rest.
( Morel laughs )
How was that just now
different from what I said?
Come on, knov.
( Knov scoffs )
Morel: Look, kid,
the minute you start calculating
the odds of winning
in nen combat,
well, it just shows
you’re missing the whole point.
In most cases,
you don’t know what
your opponent’s abilities are,
and when you’re
in a fight like that,
even the slightest hesitation
can be a matter
of life or death.
All of a sudden, having more
or less aura than the other guy
isn’t really much of an excuse.
Plus, the battle can
turn quickly and at any time.
That’s the essence
of nen combat.
Still, no matter what,
always fight like you know
you’re gonna win.
That’s what it means to have
the spirit of a nen user.
You were disqualified
the second you got scared
of your opponent’s nen and ran.
You’re worse than a loser.
Knov: Morel, that’s enough.
Netero: Is gon
sound asleep there?
Killua: No, he’s not.
He tried to attack,
so I used force to stop him,
I didn’t have time to hold back,
so I don’t know
when he’ll wake up.
( Morel laughs )
Sounds like the other kid’s
got a lot more of a future.
Knov: Morel.
Netero: It’s rather
difficult to believe
that giant chimera ants
have taken to eating humans,
yet it seems to be true,
and therefore we must attempt
to keep the casualties
to a minimum.
If we send in fighters
who aren’t strong enough,
we’re running the risk
of assimilation.
Do you understand?
Killua: Yeah.
That’s why
there are only three,
a select few.
We’re not strong enough,
not by a long shot.
Netero: We have already
placed two assassins
in the nearest city.
( Killua gasps )
Netero: Whether or not you want
to fight them is up to you.
However, if you truly
want to live as a hunter,
take them down,
and come find us.
We don’t need just any help...
Only the strong.
♪
Morel: You were disqualified
the second you got scared
of your opponent’s nen and ran.
You’re worse than a loser.
Killua: I’m no longer qualified.
- Gon: Killua.
- ( Killua gasps )
Gon: Thanks a lot.
( Killua shudders )
"Thank you"?
Why would you say that?
Gon: Well,
because you knocked me out.
It was you, right?
I mean, if i’d
lost control back there,
I would have
gotten in the way...
And if I had,
all three of us would have died.
Killua: Maybe, but I just--
I left kite back there to die.
Gon: Kite is still alive.
( Killua gasps )
Gon: He would never be beaten,
not by something like that.
But he did get injured,
and in his shape,
just trying to move
is pretty hard on him,
so he’s hiding.
He’s waiting for us
to come back.
So now we get strong,
and we find him.
We’re gonna go save kite.
♪
Killua: Gon...
You’re light itself.
Yeah. Yeah, you’re right.
( Thinking )
Sometimes you’re so bright,
I can’t even look at you.
But still,
can I stay by your side?
- Let’s go.
- ( Bird tweeting )
We’ve gotta get stronger.
♪
Colt: Prepare a freezing chamber
in the fortress!
Make it large enough to store
more than a hundred humans!
Neferpitou: To ensure
that my collection doesn’t rot.
Yup!
I think i’m pretty strong
after all
♪
( Singing in Japanese )