Narrator: Leol has pursued morel
into an underground church,
where they will now
face off in battle.
( Morel chuckles )
Gaah!
Leol: This ability only
activates when it’s raining.
Tube: Surf’s up!
Morel: Hmm. Huh?
( Rumbling )
( Grunts )
♪
( Singing in Japanese )
( Water rushing )
Leol: My tube ability
summons the ocean!
( Morel grunts )
Huh?
Leol: Well? What do you think
of my big wave? Huh?
I can wash away all your smoke
like it wasn’t there.
( Both grunt )
( Morel growls )
Leol: Yeah! ( Laughs )
Having trouble
moving in the water?
( Morel groans )
Leol: Do you like how easily
my board maneuvers
across the waves?
Just stay still,
and you’ll die even quicker.
Morel: That isn’t your ability.
Leol: Huh?
Morel: I know that power
belongs to a friend of mine!
Leol: He’s making
a boat out of smoke?
I see.
You can ride on top of it.
( Both grunt )
Leol: Hah!
Do you really think
that’s enough to tame my waves?
Morel: I already told you
that is not your ability!
Leol: Huh. This one
is one of my original moves.
( Yelling )
Vortex!
Morel: Damn it.
The current’s so strong
I can’t tell up from down.
This is bad.
I can’t move at all.
Leol: I immobilize my enemy’s
movements with the whirlpool.
Here goes!
Then finish him
with a harpoon from above.
Even from the sky,
my harpoon can Pierce
a whale deep in the sea
by traveling
at the speed of sound.
Take this!
Huh?!
♪
Wait. He disappeared?
Impossible.
The whirlpool
should have kept him trapped.
He had no way to escape.
Ah.
Bastard.
How did you do that?
( Morel laughs )
I exhaled. That’s all.
When it comes
to maximum lung capacity,
i’m confident that i’m
the best in the world.
Leol: No way.
He used his breath
as jet propulsion
to break out of the whirlpool?
Morel: Okay, then.
Looks like it’s my turn now.
Leol: What the hell
are you talking about?
The way this battle’s going,
you won’t get a turn. Sorry.
All you get to do now
is drown in my waves.
Morel: The whole time
we’ve been talking,
there are three things
that i’ve learned about you.
- Leol: Huh?
- Morel: Okay,
now the first thing
that i’ve learned
is that your ability somehow
uses the abilities of others.
Also, your headphones have
nothing to do with your ability.
They’re either
a good-luck charm,
or they’re just for show,
or you could be getting all
your orders from somebody else.
( Leol growls )
Morel: If he’s increasing
his risk by limiting his hearing
in order to upgrade his ability,
he shouldn’t be able to hear me.
Leol: What’s the third thing?
Morel: Third is your life span.
Tube once belonged to a hunter
I knew named grachan, not you.
He was helping
to exterminate chimera ants,
so I suppose
you must have defeated him,
and since you stole his ability,
you deserve to die.
This ends right here!
Time to pay
for what you’ve done!
Leol: Hang on.
That’s pretty one-sided,
don’t you think?
I was merely protecting myself
from the humans
who were hunting me,
an act of self-defense,
simple as that.
Besides, I didn’t steal
your friend’s ability.
( Chuckles )
I’m only borrowing it.
Morel: "Only borrowing it," huh?
( Scoffs )
That’s a lowlife thief’s excuse
if I ever heard one.
Huh?
Leol: I can see
that arguing with you
is just a waste of my time.
I’d like to get my hands
on his ability,
but defeating him’s
more important.
You think too much.
Right now, our top priority
is to defeat one another.
♪
I’ll say it one more time.
You don’t get a turn
in this fight!
Heavy pounder!
I’ll flood
this underground church.
My wall of water
can’t be stopped!
Good luck reaching the surface!
♪
Can you even come up?
Shall I smash your skull
with my board?
Launch my harpoon
through your gut?
Well? What’s it gonna be?
Either way, if he dares to show
his face above the water,
he’s done for.
He’s not coming back up.
Has he drowned already?
No.
He was confident
in his lung capacity,
so he can survive
for ten, maybe 20 minutes.
No, wait. It’s possible
he could stay underwater
for even longer, like a whale.
- ( Bubbles popping )
- Huh?
There you are.
Now hold still, and i’ll
stab you with my harpoon.
- ( Bubbles popping )
- Huh?
Bubbles
on the opposite side, too?
And over here.
And there.
There are bubbles everywhere.
I get it.
It’s possible
he could have formed his smoke
into a hose
with multiple branches.
That way, he wouldn’t
have to reveal his position.
Hey! How long are you
gonna stay under?!
You expect me to give up
and deactivate this? Is that it?
No, it’s not.
The bubbles are camouflage.
Did he escape?
If his lung capacity
is as great as he says it is,
he could swim out
through the twisted maze
of underground corridors
that lead down here.
I can’t let him get away.
I told welfin and bloster
to stay back
so I could take
all the credit.
( Gasping )
My head’s spinning,
and my chest hurts
is it poison?
♪
( Gasping )
My board’s gone!
I’m too unstable
to keep it activated.
( Groans )
Can’t move or breathe.
My ability stopped working,
but the water’s still here?
Is it because we’re underground?
Not good.
I let him think
he had the advantage
so I could turn
the tables on him,
but it looks like the one
who was backed into a corner
was me.
( Gagging )
Is this it?
Is this the end?
Am I gonna die here?
So he was using a hose
made of smoke
to send air bubbles everywhere.
But if this is poison,
what kind of poison is it?
Morel: That was faster
than I thought.
The poison you’ve inhaled
is lethal,
but it’s naturally found
in the air.
♪
It’s co2.
Narrator: Morel used
his immense lung capacity
to suck in the stagnant air
trapped in the church
and exhaled it with an increased
concentration of carbon dioxide.
Morel: You might
not have realized it,
but my attacks began
even before yours.
If what he said was true,
grachan should be
getting his ability back
right about now.
♪
( Bizeff snoring )
Palm: I’ll be free
to move around for a few hours.
In that time, I have to see them
with my own eyes.
I’ve watched bizeff’s movements
with my crystal ball.
I know how to get out of here.
Even if bizeff
learns that i’ve escaped,
he can’t tell the royal guards,
because he’s kept
this area a secret.
♪
( Gasping )
They’re close, right above me.
( Elevator dings )
( Gasps )
♪
( Swallows )
( Gasps )
( Gasping )
I can’t go any further, but...
( Shuddering )
( Killua groaning )
( Faint chatter )
( Gasps )
Ikalgo: Oh! You’re up.
That’s good.
( Killua groaning )
( Gasps )
Hey, octopus!
How long--and where--
ikalgo: Don’t call me that!
This is an underground hospital
for folks with roots
in the underworld.
You were out for two whole days.
Killua: Two days?
I need to get going.
Ikalgo: Whoa! Just take it easy.
Your wounds still need to heal.
( Killua grunts ) But there
are things that I have to do.
Ikalgo: Idiot!
You were on the verge of death!
You can’t
just go running off now!
You’ll need to rest before--
- doctor: Ah, look who’s awake!
- Ikalgo: Huh?
Doctor: How wonderful.
Killua: Thanks for helping,
but i’ll be checking out now.
Doctor: Not until
you pay your bill.
And the total comes
to 1.8 million Jenny.
If you can’t pay, then i’ll
accept body parts instead.
Killua: I don’t have
my wallet with me,
so i’ll wire it
as soon as I get back.
Doctor: Do you really think
that i’m stupid enough
to take an I.O.U. From you?
Until you find someone
to bring me the money,
you’re staying
right where you are.
Killua: Look,
I don’t have time for that!
Just give me your phone!
( Phone line ringing )
Doctor: It’s 10,000 Jenny
for each minute.
Killua: Quiet!
Just shut up, and go away!
Gon: Hello.
Killua: Hey, gon, it’s me.
Gon: Killua!
Where are you, what happened,
and are you okay?
Killua: I’ll tell you
when I see you.
An enemy gave me
a little bit of trouble.
I’ve been in the hospital.
Gon: That sucks,
but thanks for calling.
So you’re okay, right?
Killua: Yeah. Heading back soon.
So did anything happen
on your side?
Gon: Uh-huh. We managed
to find a really strong ally.
He and knuckle are hitting
it off great as we speak.
We have a plan that could take
the king down if it goes well.
Killua: Oh.
Gon: Let’s talk it over
as soon as possible, okay?
Killua: Sounds good, but, hey,
I need you to send money
to an account.
Do that, and we can
rendezvous later today.
( Doctor chuckles )
Gon: I guess
that just leaves palm.
Knuckle: You mean you haven’t
been able to reach her yet?
- Gon: Mm-mmm.
- Knuckle: Well,
she’s probably still
inside the palace.
Gon: What about pitou’s en?
With that, she’d be found,
maybe already has.
Shoot: I imagine that she’s
down in the underground hangar.
Its passages extend outward
for almost five kilometers,
beyond pitou’s range.
But considering that the exit is
located well within the palace,
she won’t be able to get out.
Gon: How’s Mr. Knov doing?
Morel: He’s, uh...
Probably done fighting.
But he did manage
to plant the exits,
so it hasn’t changed our plan.
( Gon grunts )
Morel: Three days to go.
( Ikalgo gasps )
His wounds,
they’re already healed!
( Gasps )
Killua: Right. I’m good to go.
Ikalgo: Uh...
- ( Door opens )
- Doctor: Okay.
Your payment
finally came through.
You’re all cleared
to leave now, so get out.
♪
( Door opens )
- Killua: What are you doing?
- Ikalgo: Uh...
- Killua: Let’s go.
Killua: We’re gonna
go join my friends.
I’ll introduce you.
( Ikalgo stammering )
But...
Killua: Fine. You don’t
have to come along with me,
but I owe you one,
so thank you.
Ikalgo: Uh, wait.
I-I mean...
Is it really okay?
I mean, i’m just a--
killua: What the hell?
Guess I was the only one
who thought
we were friends already.
Ikalgo: You’re sure?
I can go, too?
Killua: I’m sure.
Well? Are you coming or not?
Ikalgo: Yeah, i’ll go!
I’ll go with you!
Killua: Let’s just
get one thing straight.
The next time
something like this happens,
I won’t bother
taking time to thank you.
And if something
like this does happen again
and I end up helping you out,
you don’t need
to thank me either.
Friends are supposed
to help each other out.
( Ikalgo gasps )
Killua: I’m sure that you and I
will be helping each other out
all the time from now on,
but helping out your friends
isn’t anything special.
It’s expected, you know?
So let’s just cut
all the formalities, okay?
It’s not worth it.
♪
Ikalgo: Yeah, this is it.
This is the world
i’d always dreamed about,
the world I longed
to be a part of,
but deep down, I thought
it was beyond my reach,
that it wasn’t meant for me,
a world i’d completely
given up hope on!
I didn’t think
it was meant to be.
Killua, i-i’m so happy,
I could die!
Killua: Wait! What the hell
are you crying about, huh?
Ikalgo: ’cause you’re doing this
for someone like me!
( Killua groans )
Give me a break.
There’s one more thing.
Ikalgo: Huh?
Killua: The world that you’re
about to step into with me,
it’s more brutal
than what you’re used to.
It may seem similar,
but there’s a huge difference
between risking your life
and throwing it away.
( Ikalgo shuddering )
Killua: People who live
on the brink of death
never think
of throwing their lives away.
But if you can take
perfect care of your body
and drink poison that’s
barely under the lethal dose
without the least hesitation,
you can survive.
That’s what it takes.
Do you still wanna join us?
Ikalgo: How do you do it?
How do you always say
the words I most want to hear?
Thanks for the warning,
but all I see is paradise.
I’ll go, no matter the cost.
I’ve seen the other side.
I have a connection to it now.
I know it really exists...
♪
And now I know that even
someone like me can go there!
( Singing in Japanese )