Turtle ant: May we have
your permission to have names?
Queen: And what is a name?
Turtle ant:
It’s like a label, my queen,
one that can be used to identify
each of us individually.
Queen: Names,
amusing little things.
The three elite royal guards,
I shall come up
with a name for you myself.
♪
( Singing in Japanese )
Narrator: On the hunt
for the giant chimera ant,
kite’s group has finally
arrived in the mitene union.
Now they must travel
from the rokario Republic
to the neighboring
ngl autonomous region.
Driver: You heading
to the ngl, huh?
You know, they believe
that the best way to live
is as naturally as possible.
They’re pretty weird
for living out there,
but you folks are even weirder
for wanting to visit ’em.
I don’t have a clue
what’s going on there,
but i’ve already driven in
about ten big groups
just like you guys today alone.
Gon: Did you say ten?
Driver: That’s right.
Kite: So if most
of the other groups
are already arriving,
then we’re among the last.
( Horses galloping )
Pokkle: I’d guess
they’re other pro hunters.
Ponzu: You think they’re all
looking for the giant insects?
Pokkle: Yeah. Those seasoned
veterans are really something.
That must have been hard
information for them to get.
Ponzu: Bugs large enough
to attack humans,
do you think
they actually exist?
Pokkle: Well, it’s
pretty unbelievable, I know,
but when you stop
to consider the voice
they heard over the transmitter
and what it said...
Reporter: M-monsters!
Gigantic bugs!
( Static crackles )
Pokkle: It’s possible it could
be some other kind of animal.
The ngl is
one big nature preserve,
so it’s said to be inhabited
by many organisms that have yet
to be discovered by scientists.
It wouldn’t be that strange
if there were insects
that could attack humans.
Even if there
aren’t any giant bugs,
if we can confirm
the existence of something new,
it’ll all be worth it.
As a new
magical-beast hunter myself,
it’s important
that I produce results.
Now that i’m here, I have
to accomplish something.
♪
Bird ant: According
to the reports from scouts
that went out on reconnaissance
first thing this morning,
there’s a new human village
that has been discovered
in sector m.A.-18,
which is a region
in the southwest.
There are 12 houses,
as well as an estimated
20 to 60 residents there.
Cat ant: Wow.
That’s pretty big, isn’t it?
Guess there are still
a few large villages left.
Scorpion ant: I was
under the distinct impression
we’d already
cleaned out that area.
Bird ant: I shall add
this one to the list.
It will be among
our main targets today.
Now, Colt,
can you make the trip?
Colt: Yes, of course.
Cat ant: Hey, Peggy,
why aren’t you sending me out?
Peggy: Because I need you
to go to the northwest
as we had
originally planned, cheetu.
Zazan, you accompany him.
Zazan: But I just don’t believe
there are any large villages
left in the northwest.
Cheetu: And if there are,
I bet there aren’t
any strong, young humans there.
It’s a lot more fun for me
when I get to chase them around!
Colt: Cheetu!
We do not hunt for fun.
We are in service to the queen.
We need only capture
the requested number of humans,
no more and no less.
Cheetu: Yeah, yeah,
I know that already.
We’ll get the job
done right, Colt.
Right, zazan?
Zazan: I promise
to fulfill the quota,
but I don’t appreciate you
telling me how to hunt my prey.
I’ll continue
to do things as I please.
Cheetu’s right. It’s fun
to hunt humans as they run.
Colt: What did you say?
Cheetu: I guess that’s all
there is to it.
Let’s go, zazan.
Don’t get too worked up, Colt.
Learn to relax
every once in a while.
Makes things a whole lot easier.
Colt: Such insubordination.
Their squad is going
to fall apart at this rate.
Peggy: Using names
may be convenient,
at least when it comes
to leading the troops in battle,
but too much individuality
might become a serious issue.
Colt: It must be stopped before
it breaks down our command.
We simply can’t allow this.
Peggy: Yes, I agree.
It’s important
something be done.
You’ll notice
that meleoron and yunju
have yet to show themselves
at a single war council.
Colt: Hear that?
Show yourself, meleoron!
♪
Meleoron: Okay, but I
just want to be clear
that it isn’t my fault
yunju is absent.
Peggy: Were you hiding
because you thought
you would be blamed?
You are supposed to be
a squadron leader, correct?
Colt: Now where is yunju?
Why isn’t he here?!
Meleoron: You see?
It’s me getting yelled at.
That’s why I was hiding out.
Everything here
is always my fault, right?
Colt: Well, hiding the truth
makes you complicit.
- And furthermore--
- meleoron: Fine! I’ll talk!
I mean, it’s not like I wanted
to cover for him or anything.
He’s the one who ran off
to hunt the humans by himself.
Colt: He what? In what sector?
Has a new human village
been discovered?
Meleoron: That’s not it.
You remember the humans,
don’t you,
the ones who fought back,
the ones
who were armed with guns?
( Both gasp )
Meleoron: Yunju was
really worked up about it.
He said he was going to go
and make them his pets.
( Machine guns firing )
♪
( Panting )
( Man screams )
( Screams )
Yunju: Ah, come on!
You gotta keep moving,
or you might just get trampled.
Mosquito ant:
Is that all you’ve got?
Come on. Entertain us more.
Centipede ant:
That’s right. That’s right!
( Both laugh )
Yunju: Run as if your lives
depend on it!
Until you’re dead.
( Slurps )
( Chuckles )
Driver: Well, this is it, guys,
the border of the ngl.
Those two giant trees
right there
serve as both the checkpoint
and the embassy.
( Sighs ) Kinda makes you
wonder what’s out here
in the middle of nowhere.
Ah, well.
Some people are just weird,
I guess.
Kite: Prepare yourselves,
everyone.
The ants are a concern,
but the ngl isn’t
the ecofriendly group
it claims to be.
Gon: Got it.
Man: May I ask
what brings you here?
Kite: We’re on a hunt.
A biohazard-class insect
might have infiltrated
your country.
Man: Hmm.
Well, if you’re
professional hunters,
i’m certain you’re aware
that we cannot deny you entry
into our land.
Right this way.
♪
Killua: Wait. You’re using
computers and machines here?
Man: We are not technically
within the bounds
of the ngl proper yet.
This area is used for diplomacy
and trading information.
Kite: I see. Are there
similar facilities within?
Man: No, sir, not a single one.
No machines of any kind
are allowed inside the borders
of the ngl.
Man #2: Of course
visitors aren’t allowed
to bring technology in
with them either.
We’re very strict
about that kind of thing,
which means
you must remove metals,
petroleum derived materials,
and the like,
anything of that nature
on your person
before you can enter.
Lin: D-do you mean
like my glasses?
Man #2: That’s right.
If your clothes, belts, shoes,
even your underwear contain any
plastic, chemicals, or metal,
you must remove them.
Spin: That isn’t funny.
You want us to strip naked?
Man #2: That’s not necessary.
All-natural clothing
is available for purchase
just upstairs.
Man #1: And if there are
any implants inside your body,
dental implants, for example,
made of gold, silver,
or even silicon prosthetics
that cannot be removed,
i’m sorry to say,
but you won’t be allowed
to enter.
You understand.
♪
Kite: Only the five
of us are left?
I want you all to stand by
in the closest town.
We’ll return here within
two weeks and contact you.
Spin: Roger that.
Woman: The inspection area
is over there.
Of course,
there’s a physical exam,
as well as an interview.
Then once those are completed,
there will also be x-rays,
ultrasound, and metal scans.
Kite: Security’s rather tight.
Woman: It is, because people
have smuggled guns in
by hiding the parts
inside their bodies.
We often find cameras or
cell phones in people’s rectums.
Some have even trained animals
to carry laptops
across the border
once they themselves
were inside.
Well, it looks like
all of you are clean.
Man #1: Thank you all
for your Patience.
You may enter now,
and godspeed.
♪
Man #2: Welcome to the ngl.
( Wind blowing )
Kite: All right.
Now the hunt begins.
( Horses neighing )
( Horses galloping )
Man #2: Any sightings
of giant insects?
I haven’t heard
of anything like that.
And even if there were
any such creatures,
I doubt the citizens
of this country
would make much of a fuss.
If any of us are killed
or attacked by animals,
we simply accept it
as nature taking its course,
nothing more.
( Horses galloping )
Gon: Anyway, I think we should
follow along the coastline
and check out all the villages.
If we search them
and nothing unusual turns up,
then it’s probably not even
in this country.
Killua: Yeah, maybe, but that’s
assuming that those guys
were telling us the truth
back there.
Gon: They’re still following us,
aren’t they?
Killua: Yeah.
They say they’re here
in case we meet unknown tribes
and need interpreters
or intermediaries,
but they’re obviously spies.
Kite: Well, I never
expected the people here
to be of any help,
but my instincts are saying
it’s here somewhere.
♪
( Footsteps )
( Man panting )
( Groans )
Koala ant: Don’t move a muscle.
If you die,
you can’t blame me for it.
Man: You--you’re just
a mere animal!
You shouldn’t be bossing
a superior human around!
Koala ant: "Mere animal"?
I don’t understand.
Why don’t you explain
how you and I are different?
Man: Shut up!
( Gasps )
( Koala ant sighs )
Good grief.
You should answer
when someone asks you something.
Or didn’t your parents
ever teach you that?
( Man gasping )
Koala anta:
You are hopeless, old man.
( Splash )
You can try again
in your next life.
Meleoron: Aw, man.
You killed him.
How are we supposed to keep him
fresh if you kill him?
( Koala ant sighs ) I can just
make up a batch of meatballs.
I’ll serve them to her
within the day.
Humans like that one
irritate me.
They should be put
in their place.
I much prefer to see them
running terrified
for their lives.
Meleoron: Heh. Yesterday
you shot a kid in the back
while he ran away screaming,
didn’t you?
If you let me handle this,
I could have secured our prey
in a much smarter fashion
than this, I promise you.
When you said, "don’t move,"
that was meant for me,
wasn’t it?
Giving your squad leader
an order, huh?
( Koala ant spits )
Meleoron: I wouldn’t get
too cocky if I were you.
You’re lucky
i’m such a nice guy,
so i’ll let it slide this time.
If you enjoy killing so much,
you should volunteer
as a feeder.
Koala ant: It’s hopeless.
( Wings buzzing )
Colt: Damn that yunju.
( Child crying )
Rabbit ant: Shut up!
Quit your whining, or i’ll
eat you right here and now!
- Colt: Rammot!
- Rammot: Huh?
Colt: What are you doing there?
Rammot: You can’t tell?
I’m transporting the food.
Isn’t it obvious?
Colt: Then, be more selective!
I’m tired of telling you!
The one you have is worthless.
Besides, we’ve already met
our quota for the day.
You’re wasting your time.
( Rammot groans )
Then i’ll eat it myself.
Colt: What?
Rammot: Well, it’s going to be
eaten sooner or later.
♪
Colt: Put it down,
and walk away.
That’s an order.
( Rammot snarls )
- ( Child crying )
- Rammot: Hmph.
Colt: Damn it all.
So much insubordination.
Koala ant: What?
Is there a problem?
I enjoy what I do.
You want this one?
( Sighs ) I guess it’s dead,
so you can’t.
Which squadron are you from?
( Chimera ant chitters )
- Koala: Huh?
- ( Chimera ant chitters )
Koala: I see. Zazan, huh?
She is a nasty one, isn’t she?
My sympathies.
( Chimera ant chitters )
Koala: Well, you could join
yunju’s team, couldn’t you?
I hear they’re allowed to kill
as many humans as they want.
If you take this as a gift,
they’ll let all of you join up
on the spot.
Man: What in the hell is this?
Ponzu: It’s terrible.
Man #2: But who
could have done this?
( Pokkle gasps )
Man #1: A gun?
Man #2: Wait.
People are fighting with guns?
Man #1: Who, and how?
Guns aren’t allowed in the ngl.
Pokkle: They’re members
of the ngl underground
that manufactures d.D.
( Team gasps )
Pokkle: From the look of it,
these wounds
were not made by humans.
Man #2: Does that mean--
pokkle: It’s too soon
to be sure just yet...
But if the monster we seek
was responsible,
we won’t be able to handle it
with the members we have.
( Brush rustling )
Man #2: There they are!
Monsters!
( Horses neighing )
Pokkle: Ponzu! Balda! Pekuba!
Run away on my signal.
♪
Got it?
Rainbow!
Time for red arrow!
( Chimera ant wails )
Now run!
Man: Huh?
( Splash )
( Wind blowing )
Koala ant: Completely hopeless.
Ponzu: Eh?
( Chimera ants chitter )
( Ponzu yelps )
( Screams )
( Whimpering )
Pokkle: Hey, over here!
You okay?
Ponzu: Yeah.
Pokkle: Okay, then. We need to
contact the other pro hunters.
Think you can handle that?
Ponzu: No problem.
( Machine guns firing )
( Gunfire echoing )
( Gunfire stops )
( Squelch )
♪
Yunju: What?
Is that all there is?
Centipede ant: No.
There are more.
( Bullets rattle )
Mosquito ant: Oh, my!
There sure are!
I recognize
the smell of living humans!
( Cackles )
( Centipede ant laughing )
♪
( Gunman sighs )
What now, zaikahal?
Narrator: The chimera ants
continue their rampage
and have now cornered
this country’s shadowy ruler.
A storm brews in the ngl,
and gon’s group,
utterly unaware of that fact,
is heading
straight for its center.
♪
( Singing in Japanese )