♪
Gon: That’s morel’s smoky jail.
He said he’d use it
to keep pouf away from the king.
If it’s covering the entire
third floor of the tower,
then the king and pitou
aren’t there,
so where are they?
( Gon gasps )
Netero: Hmm.
( Wind blowing )
♪
( Singing in Japanese )
( Wind blowing )
Narrator: Each member
of the extermination team
has begun their battles
in their respective locations.
( Blows thumping )
( Knuckle groans )
♪
Killua: Gon.
( Gasps )
Grandpa.
That means...
That’s the king.
King: Take me.
I am fully aware
that not only are you trying
to accomplish your objective,
but you wish to do so
while keeping human casualties
at a minimum.
Your goal in creating this chaos
was to separate me from
my royal guards. Is that right?
I care not.
Take me.
♪
Zeno: Dragon head.
Netero: He’s something,
all right.
Narrator: The technique
was not intended
to hurt the king in any way.
They both realized
that the king knew this move
posed no threat to him
zeno made sure
not to infuse his nen
with the slightest bit
of mischief.
Was it out of respect
for the king or something else?
( Zeno roars )
Gon: Killua.
Pitou is right over there.
♪
Let’s go.
Killua: "Let’s go"?
Which is it?
Narrator: As much as killua
wanted to ask the question,
he suppressed the urge.
Killua: If I ask him that,
there’s no stopping it.
There’s no turning back.
Narrator: If he could only ask,
then everything
would be out in the open.
Anyone with enough experience
would easily arrive
at that next step.
But killua, fearing
that the inquiry might cause him
to lose something
he held close to his heart,
was unable
to utter a single word.
Only a few short moments
before the dragon took off,
cheetu and bloster
appeared before ikalgo.
Cheetu: Hey, it’s flutter.
( Ikalgo, flutter’s voice )
Hmm?
( Rumbling )
Cheetu: Huh?
Bloster: Huh?
Cheetu: What’s with
all that noise?
Bloster: It feels like
sir pitou’s en
disappeared again.
Ikalgo: Well, I just got
back here myself, but, uh,
it seems to me
to be an enemy attack.
Bloster: Seriously?
Cheetu: Well, I don’t think
anything else
could have caused this.
Bloster: Hmm?
What happened to your wings?
Ikalgo: Oh, uh...
I lost them
during the attack earlier.
Cheetu: You going down?
Ikalgo: Uh, yes. I have orders
from sir hagya, you see.
Cheetu: So what
should we do now?
Bloster: Well,
they didn’t tell us
we were supposed to defend
this place, did they?
Cheetu: No, but i’ve got
this brand-new ability.
I wanna try it.
( Rumble )
- ( Cheetu gasps )
- Ikalgo: Whoa!
Bloster: It’s huge!
( Cheetu laughs )
That looks fun!
I’ll check it out!
Bloster: Hey, be careful.
I think i’m gonna go
take a look around, too.
Ikalgo: Well,
I guess i’ll be off, then.
Bloster: Okay.
♪
Both: Did he say, "sir hagya"?
Narrator: Meanwhile,
in the throne room
of the central tower...
Shaiapouf:
You chose to confine me.
Do you still believe
that was the correct choice?
I wouldn’t mind
finding that out.
Morel: Wing scales.
Knov told me that those things
have a hypnotic effect.
I can’t breathe any of it in.
( Scoffs )
Shaiapouf: I see that you
have stopped talking,
the correct choice
for any good warrior.
However...
♪
He shows vigilance,
resolve, and confidence,
all of these in a ratio
of two to three to five.
His lower vigilance indicates
an abundance of confidence.
He has a strong character.
Narrator:
Spiritual message allows pouf
to get an accurate read of his
opponent’s psychological state.
He does this by diffusing
his butterfly wing scales
into the air
and making
the aura flow distinct.
Now I should introduce myself.
My name is shaiapouf,
and I serve as one
of the king’s royal guards.
The swirl of vigilance
has grown considerably stronger.
( Chuckles )
You won’t tell me
your name, will you?
If you believe
that i’m trying to trick you
into inhaling the scales,
I must inform you
that you’re sadly mistaken,
perhaps even fatally so.
And to be quite honest with you,
I find myself
feeling a bit hurt.
♪
Morel: Hmm?
Shaiapouf: But I won’t
remember when i’m reborn.
( Chuckling )
I’ll just be a moment.
( Laughing )
( Morel scoffs )
If he wants to waste time,
that’s fine by me.
I’m ready for whatever
demon or beast emerges.
♪
( Blows thumping )
Narrator:
Shoot’s reckless attacks
without fear for his own life
ironically helped him
to survive longer.
Hotel rafflesia.
While barely dodging
multiple attacks
that would otherwise
have been lethal,
shoot managed
to take a single eye
off of youpi’s shoulder.
The physical damage
was close to zero, but...
( Menthuthuyoupi roars )
Narrator: Youpi was unable
to finish off his opponent.
The strange sensation
that the eye was taken,
yet not destroyed
had a great effect
on youpi’s psyche.
Due to the series
of mysterious attacks
he could not understand,
youpi took a step back.
Menthuthuyoupi: No matter what,
I can’t let him get
any closer to the king.
Shoot: Every second
I can keep him
away from the king counts.
Narrator: Youpi and shoot’s
goals happened to coincide.
Still, this unusual
turn of events
only served
to greatly torment knuckle.
( Knuckle groans )
Endure it.
I can’t strike now.
If I attack,
i’d only be giving him proof
that there’s another enemy
he needs to worry about.
I can’t do that, not yet.
Endure it.
Narrator: Covered in blood,
shoot was taking the brunt
of youpi’s ferocious attacks.
Knuckle could only stand
on the sidelines and watch.
Staying still
was his own battle,
and no matter how much he
told himself to tough it out...
Knuckle:
Please hang in there. Please.
Narrator:
Knuckle couldn’t hold back
the tears
streaming down his face.
Knuckle: Don’t give in!
A.p.r.: It is time.
You have accrued interest.
Knuckle: What?!
Only ten seconds have passed?
There’s no way!
How much longer
do I have to endure this?
It feels like i’m suffocating
inside an iron maiden.
It’s taking all my willpower
not to run away.
This must be some kind of joke.
You’re kidding, right?
( Roaring )
I can’t take it anymore!
Narrator:
Meleoron’s first tap...
( Knuckle gasps )
Narrator: Brought
knuckle’s rampage to a halt.
Knuckle: Seriously?
It’s only been ten seconds.
But that just
might have saved me.
( Meleoron grunts )
Narrator: However, meleoron
wasn’t trying to help knuckle.
He couldn’t hold it
any longer, either.
- ( Blow whips )
- ( Knuckle groans )
Damn it.
A.p.r.: O-oopsie!
Knuckle: He barely scratched me,
but even so, it was
more than enough to pay off
my first full-strength attack
plus interest!
Shoot is risking
his life out there,
and all the while,
i’m standing here unhurt,
making stupid mistakes
left and right.
Narrator:
Youpi didn’t notice himself
scratching against anything,
nor did he notice
a.p.r.’s announcement
of returned interest.
( Knuckle yells )
Narrator: Nor did
he hear knuckle’s yell.
Knuckle: Calm down, you fool.
You’re gonna ruin everything.
This is where we want to be,
far enough away
to avoid capture,
but close enough
to rush back in.
He’ll notice a.P.R.
For a second,
but that’s nothing
we need to worry about.
Shoot’s fighting hard,
so if you wanna catch
your breath, this is the time.
( Meleoron breathes deeply )
God’s accomplice, deactivate.
Menthuthuyoupi: Hmm?
What is this,
and when did it get here?
There’s no way
I didn’t notice it before.
It just suddenly
appeared out of nowhere.
Was I hit by an attack?
No, that’s not it.
A delayed effect?
Wait. I remember this.
Or did it fulfill
the activation condition
during battle?
What is this number?
Is it a countdown, a bomb?
Can’t be.
The number isn’t changing.
Damn it! What a pain!
- ( Shoot gasps )
- ( Knuckle gasps )
Menthuthuyoupi: I just need
to get rid of the source.
Shoot: Something’s coming.
Narrator:
Despite his overwhelming power,
there was only one reason youpi
was unable to defeat shoot,
an obvious difference in talent.
Shoot: It’s fast.
I can’t get away.
Menthuthuyoupi:
One meat skewer coming right up!
♪
Huh?
( Scoffs )
He hit himself
to propel backwards.
Fine, then.
Shoot: That was close.
Narrator: The feeling that he
could win the battle at any time
emboldened youpi,
who wasn’t at all
the strategic type
to begin with.
Youpi’s analysis
was right on the Mark.
This was indeed a fight
that sooner or later
he would certainly win.
If he had made any mistake
up to this point,
it was in not realizing
that shoot was aware of this
and was fine with it.
♪
Shoot: I can still fight.
More than that,
I can still fly.
I can...
Narrator: That was true
for the time being,
yet slowly, but surely,
he was reaching his limit.
Knuckle: Hey! Youpi!
Menthuthuyoupi: Hmm?
( Shoot gasps )
Knuckle: Over here, you bastard!
Meleoron: Knuckle.
Knuckle: I’m giving him proof
that there’s another enemy
he needs to worry about.
Works for me.
That’ll distract youpi,
and, if we’re lucky,
it might even
be enough to save shoot.
Bring it on!
♪
Narrator:
After he’d taken a moment
to calm down
and regain his composure,
knuckle decided
to show himself at last.
( Singing in Japanese )