Komugi: Actually, sir,
this "detached castling"
strategy you were using
is more commonly
known as "kokoriko."
It’s one I came up with myself
’bout ten years ago.
I was so happy that a fool
like me could still give birth
to something
that was so intelligent.
I even called it
"my smart little baby."
But soon after that,
I found out how to kill it.
To think that you came up
with the same strategy I had,
I was so honored and touched,
so much so
that my heart trembled.
It felt like...
Seeing my dead baby
come back to life.
( King scoffs )
Rubbish.
I’ve lost interest.
Take a break.
Komugi: Huh?
King: Once we begin again...
Komugi: Eh?
king: You will
not get any more breaks,
so be prepared.
♪
( Singing in Japanese )
( Thunder rumbling )
I don’t like it.
During our matches,
my rhythm is the one
being disrupted, not hers.
By all rights, this should be
an unbearable indignity,
and yet, although I
find myself frustrated,
I enjoy it at the same time.
What I don’t understand is why.
My skill in self-analysis
is not yet refined.
I find it extremely vexing.
Huh?
♪
what’s this?
Did she choose not to rest?
Shaiapouf: Well...
( Komugi snoring )
King: How vile.
she shows no signs
of intelligence or dignity.
How do those beautiful plays,
those paragons of logic
flow out of her like
so much water from a fountain?
( Thunder rumbling )
Wake up! Let’s begin.
Komugi: Uh, yes. Yes, sire!
♪
King: Nine-five-one, king.
- For this match...
- Komugi: Hmm?
King: Let’s make a bet.
Komugi: Did you say, "bet"?
King: I did.
If you win,
I swear that I will give you
anything your heart desires.
Komugi: Anything? Let me see.
( Sighs )
Anything?
( Groans )
King: However...
Komugi: Huh?
King: If you lose to me,
i’ll take your left arm.
( Thunder rumbling )
Greed and fear
disrupt human rhythm.
Greed will cloud the eyes,
and fear, fear will cause
courage to shrivel and die.
Komugi: My left arm? Hmm.
My left arm? Hmm.
Mm! Should I do it?!
King: Why are you hesitating?
Komugi: Well, not to be rude,
but instead of my left arm,
do you think that it’d be okay
if just bet the same thing
that I usually bet when I play?
King: Usually? And what is that?
Komugi: I bet my life.
( King gasps )
Komugi: If I were
to lose to you,
i would much prefer
to pay the penalty with my life,
but I really
don’t want to offend you
right after you made me
such a very generous offer.
King: But I still
don’t understand.
explain yourself.
Whatever do you mean by that?
Komugi: It’s just, for me, gungi
is the only thing in my life
that i’m actually
kind of good at, you know?
In other words, playing gungi
is the only reason
I have to live.
what I mean is
professional gungi players
hardly make any money at all,
even national champions,
so the only way that you
can make any meaningful reward
is to become
the world champion
as the representative
of your nation.
to become
a national representative,
you have to win
whole tournaments.
that means
that losing even one match
is enough to disqualify you.
I come from a family of 12,
and in our home,
i’m the breadwinner,
but if I lose a single match,
i’ll become
my family’s greatest burden.
We gungi players
have this saying.
When you lose,
even the greatest king of all
becomes a mere mortal.
So if I lose to you,
i’m garbage.
Oh, but it doesn’t bother me!
It’s just what my parents
have always said.
On the day that I set my sights
on playing gungi professionally,
I told myself that i’d die
if I ever lost a match.
but I realize
that could be a problem.
King: How so?
Komugi: If I lose now,
i’ll become
no better than garbage,
and garbage is all you would get
in exchange for beating me.
That would be terrible manners
king: That doesn’t bother me.
Now, then, is there
anything that you want
if you can defeat me?
( Thunder rumbling )
( Komugi groans )
You see, the thing is
i’ve been spending
every second i’ve got
just thinking about gungi.
I’ll think about it
after I win.
King: As you wish.
she feels
neither fear nor greed.
( Chuckles )
( Laughing )
Your life, huh?
I’m just beginning to realize
that I was the one
who lacked resolve!
- komugi: Huh?
- King: I never imagined
that if you were to win,
you might ask for my life.
Shaiapouf: Sire!
King: You will be quiet.
Komugi: Me, ask for
the supreme leader’s li--
please, I would never,
ever do such a thing!
The thought never once
crossed my mind! I promise!
- King: I know that.
- ( Komugi sighs )
King: This is a personal matter.
No more betting.
That was my mistake.
Komugi: No.
( Squelch )
( Shaiapouf gasps )
King: So forgive me.
( Komugi stammers )
Shaiapouf: Sire! ( Gasps )
What have you done?
We must treat your arm.
Come with me!
Komugi: Y-your arm, sire?
King: Now continue the match.
komugi: Huh?
But w-what happened?!
Please tell me!
King: It’s your turn. Move.
Shaiapouf: Sire, please,
we must stop the bleeding!
♪
King: You heard me.
I said we’ll continue playing.
I told you that there would be
no more breaks, did I not?
Do you dare add
to my humiliation?
Shaiapouf: I shall
go summon neferpitou.
I am certain you will
still be able to play, sire,
even as your arm
is being reattached.
That is the biggest concession
I can make.
And if you refuse to accept
my offer, take my head
so that I may not live
with the shame of your death.
( Komugi gasping )
King: Fine, then.
Come closer,
and I will end you
with a single strike.
It’s your turn to play,
so move.
Komugi: I won’t.
i refuse to play
until your arm is better.
I’m very sorry.
King: I won’t say it again.
Now move.
Komugi: I will not.
If you still wish to kill me,
do it in gungi.
( Crying )
King: You little--( Groans )
Summon pitou!
Shaiapouf: Sire.
( Komugi crying )
( Thunder rumbling )
Morel: There’s no doubt.
Knov: All the puppets are gone.
Morel: Have they resumed
the sorting process again?
knov: Doubtful.
I would be very surprised.
Morel: Hmm?
Knov: At the moment,
we have the capital
completely surrounded.
The king’s well-being is
of the utmost priority to them,
so they wouldn’t go
too far from his side.
Morel: Then what’s going on?
Knov: My assumption would be
that some threat
much greater than us
has befallen the royal guard and
perhaps even the king himself.
Morel: Then that means
that this is it, huh,
our golden opportunity?
Knov: Yes...
our chance
to infiltrate the palace.
♪
Morel: But it might be
a trap, right?
Knov: It shouldn’t be.
They wouldn’t use any tactic
that might endanger their king.
Morel: They would if the king
had ordered it, wouldn’t they?
Knov: I suppose so,
but regardless,
they’ve already retracted
their long-range
radar detection.
While we can, we have to get
as close as possible.
If we want this plan to succeed,
I must create an exit
near the palace.
We’ll have to take this risk
sooner or later.
The time is now.
Leol: There. I found them.
Looks like cheetu failed.
Morel: Just don’t die.
Knov: The same to you, morel.
( Leol chuckles )
Good. They’ve split up.
Okay, i’ve found them.
we’re going to switch
to the man who carries the pipe.
Let’s go.
( Chuckles )
Neferpitou: Dr. Blythe.
king: All right,
seven-nine-one, shinobi.
Komugi: Soldier, two-three-one.
Shaiapouf: So how long
will the procedure take?
Neferpitou: Hmm.
I’d say about two or three hours
to fix it completely.
Neferpitou: And you can’t use
your puppets or en
during that time?
Neferpitou: Mm, this ability
takes an awful lot of nen, meow.
Neferpitou: Since it requires
quite a bit of your energy
and focus to accomplish,
I will serve as lookout
during the procedure,
though my en isn’t nearly
as effective as yours.
either way,
this is an important task
I cannot trust to anyone else.
Knov: There’s no evidence
they’re using en.
Luckily the rain
limits visibility.
The sun will set soon.
Once it’s dark, I will
become one with the night,
making it easier
to pick out enemy aura.
Be patient.
We need an exit near the palace,
but if i’m spotted,
it’s all over.
While I can freely
come and go as I please,
shoot and the others
can only use the exit to leave
once they enter the mansion.
If the enemy prepares
an ambush by the exit,
we’re done for.
I need to prepare three exits--
near, far, and in the middle.
We’ll need several options
spread throughout the palace
if this is going to work.
Then i’ll make several clusters
of entrances far away.
that will help us
to keep a close eye on things.
When the time comes,
we’ll decide which room
would make the best waypoint,
the one nearest the exit,
farthest away,
or the one in between.
Once that has been determined,
we’ll act.
From the enemy’s perspective,
we’ll seem to appear
before their very eyes.
We must use that opening
to separate the king
from his guards.
that’s when
our respective battles begin.
♪
We only need to win one battle,
so long as the king
is the one we get.
Under normal circumstances,
i’d already be in range
of neferpitou’s en.
I feel more dead than alive.
But I have a long way to go.
The farthest exit
still has to be
on the palace grounds,
or it won’t be
of any use to us at all.
Advance carefully, but swiftly.
Should I wait
for the sun to set?
That would be ideal, but will
the rain hold out until then?
( Groans ) I have no choice.
Should neferpitou’s en
be reactivated,
any approach
will be all but impossible.
even if I fail,
we still have other options.
Go without fear. Closer.
Closer.
( Thunder rumbling )
narrator:
Currently in the palace,
there are only three humans
the ants do not intend to eat.
First is the gungi player,
the second is Diego,
and the third human...
( Toilet flushes )
Is director bizeff.
( Door closes )
He was the country’s true ruler,
operating behind the scenes.
( Cell phone buzzes )
He was the intermediary,
and all dealings
with foreign parties
and domestic organizations
went through him.
this puts him
in the unique position
of being irreplaceable,
so he is the only human
allowed near the king.
♪
there is not
a single human guard
posted anywhere near the palace.
Because ordinary soldiers would
be powerless against nen users,
the royal guard determined that
the presence of human soldiers
would increase the risk
of enemy infiltration.
Cheetu, who has
only just returned,
is the only squadron leader
on the premises,
along with six soldier
and lesser-ranked ants.
In other words,
at the present time,
there are only three humans
and 11 ants in the palace.
The soldier ants are
the various squadron leaders’
personal favorites, and as such,
have nothing whatsoever to do
with guarding the king.
Whatever strict loyalty
once existed between the king
and his squadron leaders
has vanished entirely.
Self-interest was the only thing
keeping them there,
nothing more.
knowing this,
pitou and the royal guards
have given them duties
that are of little consequence
and are expected
to end in failure.
Lookout duty would never
be entrusted to the others.
Knov has no way of knowing this,
but his current attempt
to infiltrate the palace
is taking place
at the best time to do so
and the last.
( Fax machine beeps )
Bizeff: I managed
to survive somehow,
but there’s only so much work
I can do on my own.
( Typing )
If I don’t convince them
to provide at least
three more staffers to handle
the secretarial duties,
i’ll die of overwork for sure.
( Sighs )
( Computer chimes )
Huh?
♪
Ah?
( Laughs )
Ah.
( Gasps )
"Sinker bell."
Yes.
( Chuckles )
( Computer chimes )
Marcos: There.
Hey, palm, got a hit.
♪
Narrator: While knov
works desperately
to sneak
into the palace undetected,
palm is preparing to launch
an infiltration of her own.
( Singing in Japanese )