♪
( Gunman sighs )
What now, zaikahal?
♪
( Singing in Japanese )
Narrator: His name is gyro,
the ngl’s shadow Don.
♪
Gyro spent the first
12 years of his life
inside a construction camp.
Before he had even spoken
his first words,
he had already learned
to lay bricks and mix concrete.
His father
forced him to slave away
until gyro finally killed him
and made his escape.
His father was a quiet man
who raised gyro by himself.
After work, he would
drink cheap liquor alone
until he went to bed.
It was incredibly rare
for him to talk to gyro,
who slept on the upper bunk.
It was for that reason
he barely knew how to speak
before he was seven years old.
When gyro returned from work,
he was not permitted
to leave his bed,
the only exception
being trips to the restroom.
He was allowed to relieve
himself just twice a day
and only before 9 P.M.
The rotting wood of
the bed frame would creak loudly
whenever he would turn
in his sleep.
- ( Creaking )
- His father hated that sound.
Once, that noise caused
his father to beat him severely,
and after that, gyro learned to
sleep without moving a muscle.
He also learned
to hold his bladder at night
and kept an empty liquor bottle
by his bedside
for when he simply
couldn’t hold it in any longer.
"Don’t make trouble for others,"
his father said.
As a matter of fact,
that was the one lesson
that his quiet father
taught him.
From a very young age, gyro
did his best to adhere to it,
learning from his mistakes.
His father had never bought him
anything, not even a toy,
so this lesson
was his one and only gift.
Inside his small,
troubled world,
his father
was essentially a god,
and no matter how cruel
his father could be,
gyro continued
to idolize the man,
believing that deep down,
his father truly needed him,
a belief stemming
from two facts.
When gyro was five,
he suffered a terrible fever
that nearly killed him.
His father stayed up all night,
replacing his towels
with fresh ones.
The other reason was that his
father had never at any point
ordered him to leave,
not even once.
And these two facts filled
gyro’s young heart with pride.
Boy: You idiot!
You know why your dad
hasn’t kicked you out yet?
It’s just because
you still bring in money!
Narrator: Though he had
previously kept that possibility
locked away deep in his mind,
when the older youth
brought it to light so harshly,
something in gyro snapped.
Boiling with regret that he had
revealed his precious secrets,
he was furious with himself.
His pride gravely wounded,
a feeling of rage overcame him,
and he attacked the youth.
( Spoon clatters )
The youth had made a habit
of mocking the timid boy,
so when the boy fought back,
he went mad with anger,
to the point where
not even knocking gyro out
would satisfy him.
He stomped on the boy’s face
spat on him,
and then he uttered
the finishing blow.
Boy: When you got sick, it was
a neighbor who took care of you!
Bet you didn’t know that,
did you?
Your dad
didn’t lift a finger for you.
He was just drinking alone
like usual!
You were delirious,
so there’s no way
you could have known this,
but later that same night,
your neighbor got into a fight
with your old man.
He asked your dad what he
would do if his kid died,
and do you wanna know
what he said?
Father: It wouldn’t matter.
I don’t care
if he lives or if he dies.
Boy: Hear that? ( Cackles )
Narrator: As gyro
listened to the youth,
he witnessed
something inconceivable.
♪
His father met his gaze,
but paid him
no attention at all,
and, without a word,
turned and walked away.
That was when gyro
finally understood.
"The universe doesn’t
give a damn about me.
"No one cares if I live or die,
not even my own father.
"In other words,
my life has no meaning.
"If I live, i’ll bring in money.
"If I die, i’ll free up space
in the room. That’s all.
"My father told me
not to make trouble for others,
"but I know now that
the only reason he said that
"was so he could avoid
any inconvenience for himself.
"Those words were never
meant to help his son.
"They were solely
for his benefit and his alone.
"’others’ meant my father.
No, it meant humans."
"Don’t make trouble for humans."
"So I must not be human."
Eventually the boy stood up,
and he grabbed a nearby hammer.
♪
Nine years later,
gyro founded the ngl,
which became a nation
nine years after that
with him as its king.
More than anything,
gyro wanted to spread evil
throughout the world.
The drug d.D.
Was merely the first step
in achieving that greater goal.
Mosquito ant: Yunju!
You handed those humans over
to Colt pretty easily.
( Yunju scoffs ) I didn’t
feel like fighting them.
The food will reach
the queen either way.
All I want is to enjoy the hunt.
Gyro, huh?
Damn it.
I should have just eaten him.
Listen up!
I’m taking over this factory.
From now on,
this is my fortress!
- ( Gunshot )
- ( Birds squawking )
( Chimera ant laughs )
( Laughs )
These are so awesome!
( Pistols firing )
( Laughing )
( Gunshots, laughter echoing )
♪
Pokkle: This is bad.
These creatures
are too dangerous.
Ponzu: Look!
Pokkle: Eh? ( Gasps )
( Wings buzzing )
What the...
Hang on. Exactly what the hell
is going on here?
Colt: What?
More dead soldiers were found?
Cheetu: Yeah. Three of zazan’s
were just discovered.
Actually, one of my own
has gone totally missing, too.
Its communications
have been cut off,
and it hasn’t returned yet.
Colt: Yunju’s team dealt with
all the humans holding guns.
I cannot help but wonder
if this means
that there are other humans
who are resisting us as well.
Cheetu: Sure is starting
to look that way,
but something killed
all those soldiers.
And whatever the heck it was,
it certainly wasn’t a gun.
Colt: "Something"?
What do you think it was?
Cheetu: Now,
how would I know that?
Probably some brand-new weapon
that we haven’t seen yet.
Colt: Where are the corpses now?
Cheetu: Peggy is
checking them out up there.
Peggy: Well,
a gun killed this one.
I can tell, because the bullets
are still lodged
inside of the body.
I’m not so sure
about the others.
Colt: It appears
the skull was punctured.
Peggy: It was, but not by a gun.
I had difficulty
grasping the surviving soldiers’
explanation of the events.
The foot soldiers’
communications were simple,
yet indecipherable.
It said one human
mimicked firing a gun,
and although
no projectile emerged,
something pierced the soldiers’
skulls, killing them.
Colt: I see,
but don’t some of the soldiers
sense things around them
instead of seeing them?
Peggy: Indeed, they do,
and when we questioned them,
those soldiers claimed that they
felt a projectile being fired.
♪
So they possess a number
of abilities we do not.
These humans may be
tougher than we thought.
( Colt scoffs )
If it’s a human power,
then i’m sure
we can learn to use it,
since we’ve
inherited those traits.
It’s not a big deal.
Peggy: You don’t understand.
The humans’ real strength
lies in their ability
to learn things.
If they ever find out
that the queen is where
we’re the most vulnerable,
they will do
whatever it takes to kill her.
Hmm?
Colt: You do not understand.
We will keep her safe.
We will stop at nothing
to ensure no harm comes to her.
Right?
Peggy: Eh...
Yes, I suppose you do
have a point there.
Colt: That’s right.
I will protect her.
I will protect reina.
Peggy: Reina?
Colt: Who in the world is reina?
Peggy: Uh, I didn’t say it.
You did!
Colt: I did?
No, I didn’t say a word.
You must be hearing things.
Well, regardless, the problem is
that humans possess
multiple types of weapons
that are capable of defeating
our foot soldiers.
Peggy: Huh.
What do we do?
Colt: It’s simple.
We will take
their weapons from them
and give them a taste
of their own medicine.
Only soldiers of our rank
can use complex weapons,
but humans are fortunately
not aware of that fact.
That will
definitely frighten them.
Peggy: I see.
You are obviously
a more accomplished strategist
than I am.
Colt: Reina, huh?
( Bees buzzing )
Ponzu: It’s no use.
No one received the message.
So the other hunters
we were in contact with
are probably dead.
Pokkle: I see.
Let’s go.
Those creatures
are too much for us to handle.
We need to get out of the ngl
and tell the whole world
what’s happening here,
then form an extermination team.
Pekuba: Fine! Whatever!
Let’s just hurry up
- and get out of here...
- ( All gasp )
Or else we’ll all be--
♪
( Sighs )
( Gasps ) It’s...
Here!
( Pokkle yells )
Come on!
More will be coming soon!
Chimera ant: Hold on.
I thought I instructed you
to capture the humans alive,
didn’t I?
We’re supposed to deliver them
to the queen
while they’re fresh.
Pokkle: Wait.
That’s a human face.
Ponzu: But what is that thing?!
Balda: Fire! Open fire!
Pokkle: My orange arrow
is the fastest
of my seven
spectrum array rainbows,
and he caught it easily!
Chimera ant: What’s this?
It’s completely visible.
Are you telling me the grunts
really couldn’t see this?
How disappointing.
Oh, I get it now.
The life energy
that surrounds your body
is what fuels the weapon.
Is that right?
Oh, that’s very good. Yes.
You will make a magnificent meal
for the queen.
( Laughs )
( Balda gasps )
( Screaming )
Pokkle: Balda!
( Chimera ant hisses )
( Screaming stops )
( Pokkle shuddering )
( Chimera ant gasps )
What have I done?
I wasn’t thinking,
and I took a bite out of it!
Ohh! Mistress zazan’s going
to be angry with me again.
Pokkle: You bastard!
( Chimera ant gasps )
Wait! One moment, please!
My hands are full!
Pokkle: Take this!
( Gags )
( Groaning )
Zazan:
You’re pathetic in battle,
but that’s hardly unusual.
Chimera ant: Mistress zazan!
Zazan: Why don’t you just drop
what’s in your hands?
Chimera ant: Huh?
Oh, yeah.
- Zazan: We’re going back.
- Chimera ant: Oh?
Zazan: Well, we’ve gathered
some excellent prey, after all.
This one probably has
the nutritional value
of a thousand normal humans.
Well done, pike. Good job.
( Pike swoons )
( Gasps ) Mistress zazan!
I am ever so grateful
for your praise! You honor me!
Zazan: Don’t forget the prey.
Pike: Oh!
Of course not, mistress.
♪
Ponzu: I can’t save him myself.
I have to call for help.
There might still be time.
Even if they take him,
they probably
won’t eat him right away.
Please, take this to the hunter
with the strongest aura
you can find.
I have to get back to the border
as fast as I can.
There should be others there.
( Footsteps )
( Chimera ant laughs )
- ( Laughing )
- ( Firing pistol )
This is so much fun.
( Gobbling )
Hunting is so much fun.
♪
Kite: It’ll be risky.
( Both gasp )
Kite: You sure
you want to come along?
Gon: Yeah.
Killua: We’re professionals,
aren’t we?
Kite: Miss translator...
I’m sorry,
but we really must hurry.
Interpreter: Right.
I’m sure the horses
can gallop a bit faster
if it’s necessary.
Kite: They still
won’t be fast enough.
I want you two
to return to the border
and rendezvous with the others.
Then call the association.
These things are dangerous.
Stick: Got it.
Podungo: You be careful,
okay, kite?
Kite: I will.
Keep up,
or i’ll leave you behind.
Killua: Yep,
and right back at you.
Gon: Okay. I’m ready.
( Kite chuckles )
( Wind blowing )
Let’s go.
( Interpreter stammers )
♪
( Gon shuddering )
Killua: This is a bullet casing.
Gon: But I thought
anything mechanical
was forbidden here, isn’t it?
Kite: It means the underground
rulers of the ngl
weren’t only manufacturing
drugs, but weapons.
Killua: Yeah,
but judging by this...
Kite: This wasn’t a human.
Most likely,
it was a chimera ant.
If my instincts are correct
and the chimera ants
are using firearms now...
I hate to say it,
but it’s possible
the ngl’s underground rulers
have already been fed
to the queen.
What would happen
if the chimera ants
were born with their genes?
The ngl and the chimera ants,
it’s the worst combination
imaginable.
This will be
an unprecedented biohazard.
Narrator:
The situation has taken
a sudden turn
for the absolute worst.
♪
( Singing in Japanese )