( Chorus vocalizing )
Gon: A grassy plain stretching
as far as the eye can see.
( Gasps )
I’m being watched...
But from where?
♪
( Singing in Japanese )
I’ve gotta wait here for killua.
( Chorus singing
in foreign language )
Player: Hey,
sorry to make you wait.
Player #2: Do you feel that?
Feels like
somebody’s watching us.
Player #1: Yeah, and the gaze
is definitely human.
Gon: So i’m not the only one.
Player #1: Whoever it is
can’t be too good
if we can sense them from here,
so there’s that.
Just ignore it.
Killua: We’re being watched.
- Gon: Killua!
- Killua: What’s up?
I don’t see any towns
around here. Do you?
Gon: I don’t, but everyone
is heading the same way.
Killua: Hmm. There or there?
Gon: Wait.
How did you know that?
Killua: Because that’s where
whoever it is is watching from.
Unfortunately we have no idea
what they’re watching us for.
Gon: Good point.
Killua: Well, whoever it is,
we need to start gathering
information. Come on.
- So how did it go?
- Gon: Hmm?
Killua: Your save data,
of course.
Book.
How many cards
were inside of it?
Gon: Uh, there weren’t any.
Killua: What? Really?
Gon: But there was
a message from ging.
Killua: What’d he say?
Gon: He told me
to enjoy the game.
Killua: "Enjoy the game"?
Is that it?
The thing is, this just doesn’t
really feel like a game to me.
And book.
Gon: What do you think
about all those rules
that the girl explained to us?
Killua: Hmm.
Don’t know enough yet.
I suppose we’ll see.
( Whooshing )
♪
What was that?
Gon: Was it nen ability?
Player: Let me guess.
This is your first time
playing, huh?
Killua: Eh, who knows?
You must be a player.
You’ve got a book.
Player: You think?
Hmm.
Can’t fool me.
I know a newbie when I see one.
( Thinking )
I can use the peek card.
Killua: What the hell
is he doing?
Player: Huh.
So you two are
killua and gon, huh?
( Both gasp )
Gon: How do you know our names?
Player: That is
an excellent question.
( Chuckles )
( Thinking ) If you
don’t know about spell cards,
you don’t stand a chance.
There. That settles it.
They’re a couple of noobs
who just got here,
and they’re only kids.
This one’s too good
to waste on them.
Trace should do it.
Trace on!
- Attack killua!
- ( Both gasp )
( Player laughs )
You can’t run away from
the spells in this game, kid!
( Killua groans )
Gon: Killua, you okay?
( Player chuckles )
So it worked.
Killua: What was that?
Player: This kid is dangerous!
Return on!
Masadora!
( Killua scoffs )
- Shalnark: Shizuku. Kortopi.
- Shizuku: Hmm?
Shalnark: You got a minute?
Kortopi: Play?
Shalnark: Yeah.
Do you want to go with me?
There’s nothing to do at home
once we get there, anyway.
Shizuku: You really
want to clear this game?
Shalnark: Actually clearing it’s
not really my goal.
Shizuku: So does this relate
to troupe business?
( Shalnark chuckles ) Maybe.
( Both sigh )
Kortopi: I got it.
Shizuku: Okay.
Gon: So how are you
holding up, killua?
Killua: Oh.
I don’t feel any different.
Gon: Good,
but i’m still worried.
That guy definitely
did something to you.
Killua: There’s no point
stressing about it.
Gon: Hey, did you see
if he was using nen
when he said, "trace on"?
Killua: No. It’s probably magic
that only works in the game.
Gon: Magic? What kind?
Killua: Don’t know,
but we’ll find out soon enough.
Gon: Right.
Look. There’s a town!
♪
Killua:
Those must be the prizes.
Gon: Wow! All of ’em?!
Killua: It seems like it.
Gon: Hey, killua, look.
Killua: "Antokiba monthly
tournament schedule."
Gon: This month is
rock-paper-scissors!
Killua: And the prize
is the sword of truth.
Gon: So is that
an important item?
Killua: Probably so.
Check it out.
There, too.
Gon: You wanna play?
Killua: Of course.
Gon: Then since
we’re here anyway,
let’s enter
lots of contests and stuff.
Killua: But we should
also gather information.
( Stomachs growl )
Chef: Welcome!
Finish this within 30 minutes,
and it’s free!
You’ll also receive a gargaider
as your prize!
Your time begins right now.
♪
Killua: Old man, so do you
know how to use any magic?
Chef: What is that?
Gon: Oh, and who’s
the wisest person in this city?
Chef: Wisest? What is that?
Gon: This guy
doesn’t really know anything,
killua: Really. I bet
he’s just an npc or something.
Chef: Wow! You did it!
Here. You boys
have earned your gargaider.
Killua: 1217...
And f-185.
Gon: Hey, wait.
What does that mean?
Chef: Oh, is this
your first time seeing a card?
The left number is
the item’s card number,
and the sequence on the right
ranks how difficult
it is to obtain.
There are 10 ranks in all,
from ss to h.
F would be the third easiest,
you see!
And the number
right next to the rank
is the item’s maximum
conversion limit.
( Gon groans )
And that means
that this item card...
Killua: Yeah,
this is unplayable.
( Explosion )
( Crowd screaming, chattering )
Villager: Never seen him before.
Villager #2: That’s brutal.
Killua: He entered
the game with us.
Hey, so what happened here?
Villager #1:
His body suddenly exploded,
just blew up from the inside.
Gon: We’ve only
been playing for a few hours,
and there’s already a fatality.
The corpse is real.
He really is dead.
This doesn’t seem
like a game at all.
We really are
risking our lives here.
( Both gasp )
Gon: He vanished?
Killua: He went back
to the real world. Game over.
Gon: Hey, killua,
do you think that the magic
that guy used on you earlier...
Killua: I don’t know.
Player: Don’t worry.
There are no spells in this game
that are anything like that.
Gon: Spell, sir?
Player: Like you said,
it’s something akin to magic.
Player: One thing’s for certain,
he died
from another player’s nen.
Gon: Really?
Killua: Does that mean
the players here
are trying to kill each other?
Gon: Why would they do that?
Player: It’s player hunting.
Killua: "Player hunting"?
Player: I can explain
everything to you later.
Anyway, you two want to team up?
I know of a surefire way
we can clear this game.
If you’re interested,
follow me.
Meet the rest.
They’re waiting up ahead.
Gon: What now?
Killua: Well, sounds suspicious,
and we’re already off
to a pretty bad start.
Player: Not to be rude,
but on your way here,
didn’t another player
use an attack spell on you?
Killua: Have you been
spying on both of us?
Tell me the truth.
Player: Sure, and not just me.
Lots of people around here
keep an eye
on brand-new players
at the starting point.
If you come with me,
i’ll explain why
and tell you all about
the spell that was cast on you.
Killua: You’re sure
being pretty generous.
There’s gotta be a catch
in there somewhere.
Player: We don’t have a choice.
Once you realize
how hard this game is,
not to mention how foul
and frightening it could be,
i’m willing to bet
you’ll be a lot more happy
to accept our offer.
And you’re newbies, so you could
definitely use the information.
On your first time playing here,
take all the help you can get.
Killua: What makes you think
it’s our first time?
We could be returning players,
even veterans for all you know.
Player: Book.
That jump is all I need
to prove that you’re
both beginners.
An experienced player would have
reacted much differently to that
by summoning his own binder,
because you need spell cards
to defend yourself.
Gon: That means
the spell cast on killua...
Killua: Can’t be stopped
without a card.
Player: Even when
you’re not carrying any cards,
you should still summon
your binder.
It’s an important bluff.
Book.
Gon: So how do we obtain
our own spell cards?
Player: Well, the easiest way
is to travel to masadora,
the city of magic.
Gon: Masadora?
Attacker: Return on!
Masadora!
Gon: Hey, you wanna go?
I’m a little bit worried
about the spell on you.
Come on!
( Killua groans ) Okay.
( Crowd murmuring )
Player: Is this everyone?
Player #2: Yeah. Everybody else
turned me down flat.
Player #3: Fine.
Then let’s begin.
♪
Player #1: Just now yet another
player was found murdered.
He arrived here at the same time
as the rest of you did.
His stomach exploded.
It was the bomber again.
Gon: Who?
Player #3: His victims
aren’t killed by spells.
There isn’t a spell in this game
that’s capable
of injuring someone,
so don’t worry.
No matter what happens,
you won’t be harmed or killed
by any spell
that’s been cast on you.
Player #1: There are
40 different spells in all.
The one that was cast on you
earlier was an inspection spell,
so it has to be
either trace or cling.
Player #3: In short,
once the enemy uses
one of these on you
he will instantly know
everything there is
to know about you.
Killua: I get it.
So that’s why...
Player #3:
Some people choose to wait
for new players
by the starting point.
That way, they could cast
a spell on them quite easily.
As soon as a player
obtains a valuable card,
they’ll show up and steal it.
In some cases,
they just kill their target.
Puhat:
Like the guy who just died?
Well, it won’t be
that easy to kill me.
Player #3: No, he was
killed by someone else,
by a radical type of player
who hunts his opposition.
The man who died
was killed
by someone called the bomber.
Gon: Bomber.
Player #4: In this game,
there are only three ways
that a player can acquire
item cards they can use.
Know what they are?
Gon: Hmm. Find them yourself!
Player #5: You can also trade
for them with other players.
Killua: Or simply steal them
from other players.
Player #4: Yes. Those are
the three possible ways.
However, the number of players
stealing from others
has increased.
♪
That’s because of the card’s
acquisition difficulty
and conversion limit.
Players who can’t obtain
cards themselves
often choose to take them
from others.
If those players resist,
they’re killed.
Their ring disappears,
and the cards are lost,
but it increases
the conversion limit
for that type of card.
If you kill a player,
you can’t take his cards.
That rule was put in place
to prevent players
from killing each other.
Player #1: But lately
it’s been backfiring.
It’s been over 10 years since
this game was first released.
If no one can find
a way to beat it,
the killing will only continue.
That’s why all of us are all
trying to end this mess!
We need more allies
to clear the game!
That’s where you come in.
Puhat: How do you
plan to obtain cards?
One, find them,
two, trade for ’em,
three, steal ’em.
Which are you gonna do?
Player #1: Steal them.
Player #5: I have to assume
we’ll be using all three,
but that’ll be
the primary method.
Puhat: Hold on.
So you’re still gonna use force?
Player #1: No! We refuse to use
violence to achieve our goal.
- Player #5: Spells.
- Players: Hmm?
Player #5: You just
use spells. Correct?
- Player #1: That’s right.
- ( Puhat scoffs )
Player #1: There are spells that
exist for taking others’ cards,
as well as cards
that defend against them.
We plan to monopolize
those spell cards.
We’re going to use the very same
card conversion limit
that’s been frustrating us.
It’s the only way
to clear the game.
Player #3:
I’ve met a lot of players,
and they’ve all reached
the same conclusion.
Every card you find will be
taken from you eventually.
Player #4: Because that’s
what the game is based on,
taking cards from each other.
Player #6:
We take cards from others
while mitigating our own risk
of losing cards.
Puhat: You’re leaving out
something important, aren’t you?
How you gonna split the reward
money once you clear the game?
Player #6: Good point.
Mr. Battera hired
all of you guys, didn’t he?
Puhat: You knew who we were
when you found us?
Player #6: Yeah. You see,
Mr. Battera hired all of us
to play the game, too.
Player #1: That means
the reward will be 50 billion.
We’ll split it
between everyone who helps us.
Player #4: We have 53 players.
Two months to collect
the remaining spell cards,
one to get the cards we need--
three months to finish.
Player #3: Of course,
if you decide to join us,
we’ll remove any spells
that were cast on you.
Puhat: I’m in.
Can’t say I like the idea
of splitting the 50 billion,
but I do like the idea
of clearing the game
in three months.
Player #3: What about you?
Player #5: I have a question.
So if I get
an ss rank card on my own,
what’s my cut, roughly?
Player #1: Ss?
For one of that rank,
it’s about 500 million.
Player #5: Okay. I’m in.
Player #1:
What about you, kid? You in?
Gon: Killua, sorry.
Killua: For what?
Gon: Count me out.
I’m playing on my own.
( Killua gasps )
Well, you guys heard the boss.
I gotta pass.
Hey, gon, wait up!
Player #4: What about you?
♪
Player #1: First we’ll need you
to exit the game
so the spells placed on you
can be removed.
Once you’ve reentered the game,
just wait for us
by the starting point.
We’ll come get you.
Player #3: And if you have
any cards in your free slots,
i’ll need for you
to give them to me now.
Player #5: Why’s that?
Player #3:
When you leave the game,
the cards
left in your free slots
disappear completely.
Puhat: Yeah, but your data
automatically saves
when cards are put into or taken
out of the specified slots.
Player #3: That’s true,
but your data disappears
if you don’t return
within 10 days.
Player #1: And if you don’t
return to the game before then,
unfortunately we’ll have
to assume that you gave up.
Got it?
( Whooshing )
Player #1: Don’t worry.
A friend is joining us.
Player #7: We don’t know
if anyone’s watching.
Let’s begin.
First off,
i’ll use the leave card.
Killua: Hey! Wait up, gon!
You wanna tell me
what that was all about?
( Gon sighs )
Sorry, killua,
but I guess I just
couldn’t take it anymore.
Killua: Okay, but I still don’t
get why you’re apologizing.
Gon: Because you’re gonna be
stuck with that spell
for a while,
and it’s all my fault.
Killua: Okay. I get it now.
Look, it’s no big deal.
Gon: It is! You’re playing
this game ’cause of me.
You’re only here
to help me find my dad.
Killua: You’re wrong.
I’m playing this game,
because...
So anyway, why’d you get so mad?
Gon: It’s because they said
mean stuff about ging’s game,
how it’s all based
on killing and stealing cards,
and I guess
it really ticked me off.
I want to do what ging said
to do and just enjoy the game.
When I first got here,
I knew it wouldn’t be easy,
but I wasn’t afraid,
because I thought--
well, I figured all the players
genuinely enjoyed the game,
you know?
People actually die here,
but the game, it’s not scary.
It’s that players
hurt each other
all over getting some cards.
That’s the really scary part.
Killua: Really?
I think it makes sense.
Gon: Hey, you really mean that?
Killua: It’s dangerous,
but it’s just meant for hunters.
Gon: Still...
Killua: Killing is wrong, sure.
No argument on that part.
But what if two players
each put forth a card
and the one who wins
a battle with defined rules
gets to keep both?
Gon: Uh, that’s okay.
Killua: See?
When that guy cast a spell on me
and those guys
start their strategy,
they’re only following
the rules of the game.
( Gon grunts )
Killua: But to be honest,
it kinda feels
like they’re chickening out.
Look, forget about them,
all right?
Let’s just enjoy the game
by ourselves.
- Gon: Killua...
- Killua: Hmm?
Gon: Thanks a lot.
I’m glad you’re here with me.
No...
I’m really glad
I met you in the first place.
Killua: Idiot.
This is embarrassing!
Gon: No, it’s not.
How can it be embarrassing
if I mean it?
I’m sorry, gon,
but you’ve got it backwards.
I’m the one
who’s glad I got to meet you.
I really am.
Girl: I see. So that’s why.
The friendship and innocence
of two young boys
is such a beautiful thing.
It would be so much fun...
To ruin it.
♪
Narrator: Gon and killua have
reaffirmed their friendship.
But what about
the little girl watching them?
Who is she,
and what does she want?
( Singing in Japanese )