♪
Player: Don’t worry.
We didn’t come here
to interfere or anything.
Player #2: You might say
we’re here to assist.
Gon: Wait. To assist?
Player #1: That’s right.
If we get
the top score on the quiz
and obtain the final card,
we’ll sell it to you
for 2.5 billion.
That’s just 5%
of your total reward,
a pretty reasonable price,
don’t you think?
( Killua gasps )
Oh, yeah. They don’t know
about battera yet.
( Both grunt )
Killua: Works for us,
if you guys win.
Is that why they’re all here,
for the chance
to sell us the last card?
Bisky: With the game
coming close to the end,
they’re probably
hoping to get some share
of the reward money
for themselves,
and it looks to me
like they’re all planning
to take the quiz in teams.
So what should we do?
Gon: Well, I think that we
ought to do it by ourselves.
Killua: Yeah, and whoever gets
the lowest scores
gets punished!
Gon: Okay, i’m in!
( No audible dialogue )
Bisky: Honestly,
they’ve got guts.
They just finished
a life-or-death battle,
and now they’re facing the final
event with such confidence.
I’m willing to bet
that those two
enjoyed this game
more than anyone else.
Best of luck, boys.
♪
( Singing in Japanese )
Narrator: The quiz contest,
open to all players,
is officially under way.
Woman: Ladies and gentlemen,
the quiz is about to begin.
Question one--a village elder
provides you an important clue
about card number one,
plot of forest.
Is his name a, hira,
b, hida, c, hiso,
d, mayu, or, e, hima?
Killua: Damn it,
i’m stumped already!
Five choices?
( Binder beeps )
Woman: What must you do
in order to acquire number 17,
angel’s breath?
( Footsteps )
♪
Exorcist: I caught the bomber.
Woman: Number 84,
the paladin’s necklace,
is offered as a prize
in which monthly tournament?
Gon: Yes!
Okay!
♪
Woman: Now for
the final question.
What is the name
of card number zero?
A, ruler’s banquet,
b, ruler’s invitation,
c, ruler’s welcome...
- ( Both groans )
- Killua: What was it?
Gon: Whew.
Heh.
Woman: The quiz is over.
I will now announce the player
who received the top score.
♪
With a total of 87
out of 100 points...
The winning player...
Is gon.
Gon: Huh?
- ( Laughs )
- Killua: Yeah!
We have all 100 cards!
( Goreinu chuckles )
( Bisky giggles )
Player #2: You did it.
Player #1: I hate to say it,
but congrats.
- You deserve it.
- Gon: Thanks a lot.
That means killua’s
gonna get punished.
Killua: Damn. Wonder
how many total points I got.
( Bird screeches )
♪
Gon: "Ruler’s invitation"?
Killua: It looks
like only the one
with the badge is invited.
So I guess limeiro
is the capital?
And do I have to go there
all by myself?
Killua: We’ll wait for you
outside the castle.
( Player #3 laughs )
Player #4: Hey,
he really got it, huh?
That kid
collected all the cards.
Player #3: Okay, then.
Let’s have a contest.
Winner gets all your cards.
Player #4: Sorry, but you
don’t have a choice.
( Player #3 laughs )
( Player #4 laughs )
( Both laughing )
Both: Huh?
( Blows striking )
♪
Gon: Then i’ll take
an accompany card.
Killua: Wait. That won’t work.
Not one of us have
been to limeiro before.
Bisky: We should use drift,
since we’ve never visited
the other cities before.
Killua: In that case, i’ll use
drift to go to limeiro,
then come back here
for you guys.
Gon: And accompany
should work after that.
Killua: Drift on!
( Gasps )
Bingo.
Gon, let’s go.
Gon: Yeah!
Killua: Accompany on! Limeiro!
Player #1: Those kids
are really amazing.
They actually beat
the bellam brothers.
Player #2: Well, yeah,
of course they did.
They beat the bombers,
didn’t they?
Exorcist: It’s true.
Those boys
are considerably stronger now
than they were when I
first encountered them.
Even so, they’re still weaker
than genthru in raw power.
Their strategy
must have been flawless.
Well, no matter.
I’ll let you have the reward
for clearing the game.
Magnetic force on!
Chrollo lucilfer!
I’ll be heading back
to the real world now
to make a fortune
on an exorcism.
♪
Bisky: Wonder what he’s feeling.
Killua: What do you mean?
Bisky: I mean he might
actually meet ging, right?
The father he’s been
searching for all this time.
( Killua chuckles )
Man: Welcome, sir,
to greed island castle.
( Knock )
Man: This way.
( Gon gags )
♪
Whoa! What a dump!
Man: I’ve brought gon,
the top scorer.
Man #2: Huh? Oh, hey!
I’ve been waiting for you, kid!
So I hear
you’re ging’s son, right?
Well, go ahead,
and take a seat, huh?
Gon: Okay, but where
do you want me to sit?
Man #2: What?
There’s no space over there?
Then, just make some.
Like this!
( Laughs ) Oh.
Ooh, how long
has that been there?
( Grunting )
Uh...
Hang on. Where did I put it?
Aha! Here it is!
Gon: Eh?
Man #2: There you go,
ruler’s blessing,
the reward for whoever
gets the top score.
How about it?
Isn’t it the coolest?
I bet you’re surprised.
Are you surprised?
There are about 10,000 people
in this city,
so there’s a real good chance
that one of them is--
wait. Did I get your hopes up?
Did I?
Well? Or maybe
you were thinking
your dad ging
could be the ruler, huh?
Gon: I didn’t think that.
I never even thought that he
would be here on the island.
Man #2: Oh, is that so?
That’s good, then.
You know, ’cause he’s not.
- Man #1: Mr. Dwun...
- Dwun: Huh?
Man: Can we please move on now?
Dwun: Yeah, sure. That’s my bad.
( Gon sighs )
Dwun: Listen up.
So you’ve actually collected
all 100 cards that
"greed island" has to offer.
Well done! That milestone
triggers a new event.
Let me see.
- Ah, here it is!
- Gon: Huh?
( Dwun blows )
There. Now open it up.
This case has slots
where you can place
three specified-slot cards,
but that’s not all.
You can take all three of them
back with you
to use in the real world.
However, just so you know,
you can’t take multiple copies
of the same card.
You have to choose from one
of the specified-slot cards
there in your binder,
but you can pick
any three you like.
Gon: Hmm.
Dwun: Okay, you’ve reached
the end of the game,
so you get to make a choice.
You want
the normal, generic ending
or the one that’s just for you?
Gon: There’s one for me?
Dwun: Yep, that’s right.
What’ll it be? What’ll it be?
Gon: Hmm.
I’ll take the generic one.
Dwun: Oh, yeah? Why that one?
Gon: Well, I didn’t
clear the game all by myself,
and if it’s generic, my friends
can watch, too, right?
Dwun: Ah. Okay, I see. I see.
- Man: Mr. Dwun...
- Dwun: Huh?
Man: Would you please
stop teasing our guest already?
I’m sorry,
but there’s no such thing
as an ending
tailored just for you.
Gon: Uh, there isn’t?
Man: ’fraid not,
but we were given permission
to tell you a few things
after you’d beaten the game.
Gon: Huh?
Man: How rude of us.
We’ll introduce ourselves.
My name is list. This is dwun.
Dwun: And as you
probably know by now,
both of us are friends
with your old man.
List: This game
was created by ging
along with ten of his friends.
The name "greed island"
was only decided upon
because it incorporates
the first letter
of each of their names.
Your father was in charge,
so we wanted to select
a word that began with "g,"
and it wasn’t long
before we settled on "greed."
Have you met razor yet?
Well, he’s the "r,"
and i’m the "l."
The woman who explains
the game at the beginning
is the twin of the woman you see
when leaving the island--
eeta and Elena.
Both of their names
start with "e."
Dwun: See that? And then
we’ve got the letter "d."
You wanna hear it?
Wanna hear my story?
Well? Well? Well?
Gon: Uh, yeah, okay.
Dwun: Then pay attention.
Here’s the thing.
Your father ging is...
( Gon gasps )
Dwun: Your dad...
Is a huge jerk, a huge jerk!
( Growls )
My name is dwun. You got that?
And what do you think
the first letter is?!
Gon: Uh, isn’t it "d"?
( Dwun wails )
I can’t believe it.
You, too, huh?
Makes sense, I guess.
I mean, you are ging’s son.
Gon: I thought we were
talking about the letter "d."
Dwun: It’s "w," okay? "W"!
W-d-w-u-n-e spells wdwune!
And that was my name!
But even my oldest friends
in the world
thought it started with a "d."
How do you like that?
So when we all decided
on the name of the game,
I was perfectly clear.
My name starts with a "w,"
and that’s final!
But what do you think ging said
when I told him that, huh?
Ging: Really?
Then just ditch the "w."
Starting now, your name
is d-w-u-n. Okay, dwun?
( Dwun growls )
Isn’t that unbelievable?!
He went and changed my name
without even asking me
about it first,
just so he didn’t have to change
the title of the stupid game!
List: What’s even more amazing
is that only a minute later,
ging already had
dwun’s name legally changed,
and all he needed
was a phone and a computer.
Dwun: Eh, worse than that,
he took the "e" off the end,
because--get this--he thought
it was too confusing.
List: But your luck
has gotten much better
as a result, hasn’t it?
Dwun: Well, I guess so.
I’ve never been healthier,
and i’ve been eating...
♪
( Crowd cheering )
( Gong )
( Killua gasps )
Gon: Once I pick
the three cards I wanna keep,
they say i’m supposed
to go to the harbor.
Bisky: So what
about your father?
Did they tell you anything?
Gon: Yeah, but they couldn’t
tell me where he is right now,
’cause they don’t know.
Bisky: I see.
Then I guess the game
didn’t have any clues
for you after all.
Killua: Well, no surprise,
since that’s what his message
said to begin with.
Gon: Yeah, that’s true.
Bisky: So let’s get back
to the three cards.
Which ones will you take?
Killua: How about
we each pick one
and then go from there?
Bisky: I know my pick,
blue planet!
This is still the one I want!
( Squeals )
I can’t wait to hold you
snuggly in my arms.
Which one do you
want to pick, killua?
Killua: Hmm.
I’m still thinking.
Have you got one yet, gon?
Gon: Mm-hmm.
I think so, anyway.
Killua: Really? Which one?
Gon: Hold on. Let me see.
This one.
Bisky: Which one?
- ( Killua gasps )
- Bisky: Huh?
Wait. Why would you
choose this one?
Killua: Hey, I get it.
That does make sense.
You are only allowed
to take specified-slot cards.
Yeah. Sounds fun.
So when did you think of it?
Gon: Mm, as soon
as I saw it, actually.
Killua: But this one’s
not gonna be enough.
Gon: Right.
We’ll need this one, too.
Bisky: What?
Gon: I think it’ll work. Do you?
Killua: Mm-hmm. Oh, yeah.
And this is the only way
to pull it off.
Bisky: Wait.
What’s the only way?
What are you two talking about?
Killua: You get the blue planet.
You okay with that?
Bisky: Tell me what you’re
talking about right now!
( Seabirds calling )
Elena: Congratulations
on clearing the game.
And now choose
three specified-slot cards
from your binder,
any three that you desire.
You’ve chosen number two,
strip of beach,
number 81, blue planet,
and number 84,
paladin’s necklace.
Are you positive that these
are the three cards you want?
Gon: Yep.
Elena: All right.
I will now return your ring.
Very nice work.
Gon: Thanks a whole lot,
miss, uh--miss Elena.
( Elena giggles )
So you remembered my name.
Thank you for that.
( Gon chuckles )
Elena: Goodbye now.
( Sighs )
( Whoosh )
Bisky: Welcome back.
Gon: Thanks.
What do you think?
Are we back
in the real world now or what?
I can’t tell.
Killua: Well the game was part
of the real world, remember?
Bisky: Hurry up,
and get your binder out.
Let’s get this party started.
Gon: Book!
( Bisky laughs )
Gain!
Yay! This is it!
This is the one
that I really wanted!
I’ve been dreaming
about you for so long.
( Laughing )
Ah, i’ve never been happier!
Now what should I name it?
Bluey? Or maybe planetty?
- ( Killua groans )
- Bisky: Planette?
Oh, yes, yes! That’s the one!
Uh...( Chuckles )
( Clears throat )
So what about the ones
you two picked?
Happy with your decision?
Killua: Yeah.
We chose the best ones. Right?
( Gon grunts )
Killua: Well, should we do it?
Gon: Yeah!
And gain!
♪
Killua, i’ll take it.
Yes! It really worked!
Killua: It sure did.
Bisky: Oh, now I get it.
So you just used transform
to turn accompany
into a specified-slot card,
and then you used the paladin’s
necklace to revert it.
That was some clever thinking,
you guys!
But I have to say
i’m surprised
you would go to all that trouble
for an accompany
instead of choosing
another specified-slot card.
Gon: Yeah.
It’s just if I hadn’t been
the first to enter the game,
then I wouldn’t have noticed,
so I guess it was
- a good thing that I was.
- Bisky: Huh?
Killua: Do you remember when
we played rock-paper-scissors?
Bisky: You mean jan-Ken?
Killua: Yeah.
Gon: See,
I was the first person
to enter the game,
and while I was standing there,
waiting for killua,
there was nobody else around.
That means the first person
I met in the game
should have been the second
to show up, Mr. Goreinu.
But he wasn’t.
When I checked my binder,
it said that there was
somebody i’d met before him.
Ging is spelled g-i-n-g.
Bisky: Oh, I see!
So "nigg" is an anagram.
♪
Gon: My guess is that
when I was just a baby,
I must have come here with ging.
Maybe this was his way
of trying to tell me...
If i’m ready to give up
everything I have
and go find him,
then I have to get strong enough
to clear the game.
Bisky: You really are tenacious.
It’s impressive.
Well, what are you planning
to do once you find ging?
Gon: That’s easy!
- I’ll introduce him to killua.
- Killua: Huh?
Gon: I’ll tell him he’s
my best friend in the world!
Killua: You what?! Shut up!
That’s embarrassing, man.
( Bisky crying )
- Really?
- Killua: Hmm?
Bisky: Ohh. Oh, stop.
Gon: Huh?
( Bisky blows nose )
( Sobs ) I can’t take it!
It must be my age, but it’s
so easy to make me cry!
( Blows nose )
Gon: Oh, hey,
why don’t you come with us
to see ging, bisky?
Bisky: Thank you,
but I think i’ll pass.
I’m not interested
in men with kids.
Gon: Okay.
Bisky: If I stay much longer,
i’ll get too attached to them,
like a parent.
Gon: I guess that’s it, then.
Take care, bisky.
Bisky: I will.
You boys, too, okay?
Gon: Thanks so much
for everything.
Killua: Osu!
♪
Bisky: Hm.
Gon: Accompany on!
Nigg!
( Waves crashing )
( Bisky sighs ) Bye, boys.
( Both gasp )
♪
Narrator:
Gon has cleared the game
that his father created,
becoming much stronger
in the process.
Is the one waiting before him
really ging,
or is it someone else?
( Singing in Japanese )