Gon: Knuckle is--
he’s so...
He’s so kind!
( No audible dialogue )
He doesn’t have to teach me,
but still,
he keeps giving me advice.
He’s guiding me,
teaching me how to get stronger.
Bisky: Every time
you face an opponent
you perceive
is stronger than you,
you fight to escape, not to win!
♪
One day, you will
leave gon behind to die.
And tomorrow...
If you can’t defeat shoot...
You must stay out of gon’s life.
♪
( Singing in Japanese )
Narrator: As they
prepare at long last
to challenge
knuckle and shoot to battle,
gon and killua
are deep in thought.
Knuckle: The loser...
Gon: ...Gives up their tile
to the winner.
knuckle: Gon,
just as i’ve promised,
i’ll give it my all...
From the very beginning!
Gon: I can’t compete
with him in speed.
I have to be ready
and risk getting hit...
And counterattack.
♪
Can’t watch him.
I gotta feel him...
Through my aura!
( Groans )
a little late,
but I sensed his approach.
But I don’t get it.
What’s going on?
there’s a power
that’s coursing through me.
Eh?
Creature: Hello. It’s time.
You’ve accrued interest.
( Gon gasps )
Hey, what is this thing?
Knuckle: Pretty confused,
aren’t you?
I just lent you some of my aura.
Gon: You can do that? Seriously?
Knuckle: And I charge
10% interest.
That’s for every...
Ten seconds!
( Cash register dings )
Pay me back fast,
or you’ll go bankrupt.
Creature: It’s time now.
You’ve accrued interest.
Knuckle: I call this hakoware,
bankruptcy, chapter seven.
that’s a.P.R.,
amortizing power redirector.
Attacking a.P.R.
Is a waste of time.
He’s just here to announce
the interest increase.
he’s harmless
and indestructible.
( Chuckles ) Though he
can be a bit annoying.
A.p.r.: It’s time now.
You’ve accrued interest.
( Gon gasps )
It still doesn’t hurt,
not one bit.
I just feel another rush
of power instead.
A.p.r.: It’s time now.
You’ve accrued interest.
( Gon gasps )
Hey, it’s almost doubled!
knuckle: Of course,
because I lent you 180 aura.
Gon: 180 aura?
What does he mean?
What are these numbers?
knuckle: Looks like
you’re drawing a blank there.
180 aura is simply a numerical
expression of life energy.
Aura accumulates in the body,
and your maximum aura output
potential, or m.O.P.,
varies according
to your training.
Also there is a limit
to how much aura
you can release at one time,
which can be increased through
an intense training regimen.
So your p.O.P.,
the potential aura output power
inside you, doesn’t matter.
If you haven’t trained enough
to increase your a.O.P.,
the actual aura output power,
you’ll be
at a huge disadvantage.
Get it, fool?
it seems to me
the Max aura output potential
you can use through Ken
is about 1,800 aura.
when you’re
preparing for battle,
you usually expend approximately
one aura for every second.
once in combat,
as you use gyo, ryu, Ken,
all highly advanced techniques
that use a lot of nen,
your rate of expended aura
increases by six to ten times.
The stronger your technique,
the more aura you use up.
Got that, fool?
But your aura control’s
still weak,
so you’re burning up
ten aura every second.
that’s 600 aura gone
for every minute of battle.
Think back to yesterday’s fight.
You ran out in 20 minutes.
That means in an ordinary
one-on-one fight,
you used up 12,000 aura.
( Gon whimpers )
Knuckle: And you used jajanken
four times!
your a.O.P.
Is around 1,800 aura,
but at the exact moment
that you yelled, "jan,"
to activate the attack
the aura focused
in your fist was over 2,000.
That’s due to its long windup,
as well
as your defensive sacrifice,
both of which are done
to focus aura in your fist.
A special provision
covers such risks
that are often attributed
to special attacks.
You spent around 5,500 aura
in your first three uses
of jajanken alone.
That puts your total
consumed aura at 17,500.
( Gon whimpers )
Knuckle: As for the fourth shot,
right before your "round 2" hit,
you ran out of energy.
Actually following through
with the technique
uses twice
the activation amount,
which means you used
about 4,000 aura.
the amount of aura used
is the same for rock and paper.
however,
paper falls into a category
that you haven’t practiced much,
so you used up 4,000 aura
on a weak attack,
one that probably
only had the strength
of a 500-aura attack.
So your maximum p.O.P.
Is approximately 21,500 aura!
( Gon groans )
( Sizzling )
That wasn’t the kind of attack
I was expecting.
( Knuckle laughs )
Not good with numbers, are you?
That’s fine, because i’m
just getting started,
so you better listen, fool.
Gon: Uh...
knuckle: Whenever
your total accumulation
of borrowed aura,
including interest,
exceeds your current remaining
potential aura output power...
You will go bankrupt!
Aura works like a bank account.
keep spending,
and your balance decreases,
but the interest
just keeps on accumulating.
It’s been a few minutes
since we started this fight,
and you’ve spent at least 2,000.
Take a look.
( Gon gasps )
It’s huge!
And that’s not all.
It’s three times
what it was before?
That can’t be right.
It’s way too high!
it’s only been
two or three minutes!
Knuckle: 120 seconds, but close,
and it’s a perfect example
of how debt
can snowball out of control.
( Beeping )
A.p.r.: It’s time.
You have accrued interest.
knuckle: Even with
the 390 aura i’ve lent you,
you’re under 20,000.
Your debt will continue
to grow and grow.
Even if you stand
perfectly still,
in four minutes and 20 seconds,
just 260 seconds,
you will go bankrupt.
Gon: Okay, then what?
Knuckle: A.P.R becomes I.R.S.,
individual ren suppressor,
and haunts the debtor
for 30 days
while the target
remains in a state of zetsu.
( I.r.s. Laughs )
Knuckle: In short,
you won’t be able
to use any nen at all.
But it’s too late
to back out now, fool.
( Gon gasps )
♪
That’s why he didn’t use
this ability before.
He held back for my sake.
Hey, knuckle...
( Thinking)
Thank you.
( Aloud )
Here I come!
Knuckle: That one
was around 150...
Give or take.
( Gon gasps )
Knuckle: You returned
150 aura to me,
but I just lent you
another 180,
which increases
your loan by 30,
so what are you gonna do now?
And until your debt is repaid
and in full, I won’t suffer
even the slightest damage
from your attacks.
A.p.r.: It’s time.
You have accrued interest.
Knuckle: Come at me, fool!
If you just stand there,
you’ll go bankrupt anyway!
You managed to land more hits,
but ultimately you only repaid
about a hundred of the aura
that you owe me.
A.p.r.: It’s time.
You’ve accrued interest.
Knuckle: That’s just
a drop in the bucket.
You still haven’t even paid off
half the accrued interest.
i won’t let you
launch jajanken again.
Once your debt goes over 10,000,
my victory’s assured.
A.p.r.: It’s time now.
You’ve accrued interest.
( Gon gasps )
♪
( Shoot breathes deeply )
( Killua grunts )
What the hell is that?
Don’t be afraid of him.
Neither of us knows anything
about each other’s abilities.
Shoot: You should know
I take no pleasure at all
in hurting people.
( Killua gasps )
Shoot: That’s precisely
why I chose an ability
that only activates
whenever damage is inflicted.
it causes me
to be more selective.
I only use it on those
I don’t mind hurting.
However...
( Killua gasps )
♪
the two of you
helped me realize something.
There are times that it
becomes necessary to fight
as a sign of respect
for your opponent.
Killua: Three floating hands?
They’re floating, but how?
What’s his ability?
Should I attack him first?
Calm down.
Use gyo to check.
He’s not using in.
Those three hands
really are floating,
which means more than likely
he’s a manipulator.
That cage is a mystery, too.
He doesn’t need it
if he plans to use
those flying hands to attack.
In other words...
I can’t let them touch me.
Shoot: Yo-yos, huh?
First let’s see
what you’ve got.
( Killua gasps )
( Shoot gasps )
Excellent handling.
( Killua gasps )
He’s fast.
Were the hands just decoys?
( Illumi echoing )
jump back.
( Killua gasps )
Bisky: Every time you face
an opponent you perceive
is stronger than you,
you only fight to escape
and not to win.
♪
Killua: No. I have
to do better than that.
Electricity.
( Groans )
I couldn’t launch my attack.
my body,
why can’t I get it to move?
Is this my curse?
Shoot: His reaction was slow.
Did something happen?
I wonder.
Stop. Don’t think about it.
It’s a bad habit.
his circumstances aside,
I must do my best to beat him.
otherwise,
i’m only insulting him.
Killua: He’s strong and fast.
He probably has me beat
in every category.
♪
Illumi: That’s right, killua.
That’s the way.
Don’t fight an enemy
you can’t defeat.
Killua: I have to stop
thinking that way!
Bisky: Do you see your weakness?
You give up far too easily.
Even against enemies
of equal strength,
you think, "he’s tough,"
or, "it’d be dangerous
if he did this."
Then you give up at even
the slightest disadvantage.
you would run,
because you think like a loser.
It’s a problem, but I realize
it’s not one of your making.
It’s the fault of whoever
taught you how to fight.
A habit that’s as deeply
ingrained as this one is
will be difficult to break,
but one thing’s for sure.
one day, you will
leave gon behind to die.
Illumi: Forget it.
you know
you’ll never defeat him.
( Killua gasps )
My left eye.
The left side of my face,
it’s gone.
Shoot: A much better
reaction time.
Could it have been
a fluke earlier?
Illumi: If you’re hurt
and you don’t know why,
get as far from the enemy
as you can.
Killua: Looks like my curse
just saved me,
but still, it’s not good enough.
Bisky: You need to overcome
this bad habit right away.
get way out
of your comfort zone,
and take a big risk for once
by challenging
someone more powerful.
Killua: I have to fight...
♪
To win!
( Gasps )
I’m blind on the left.
Again?
Shoot: Those were
very good moves.
killua: No!
I’m just running away!
I’ve never truly fought,
and this is no different.
bisky: Tomorrow,
if you can’t defeat shoot,
you must stay out of gon’s life!
Shoot: Eh?
( Killua yells )
I won’t run anymore.
Take this.
Shoot: Electric shock?
( Killua gasps )
Shoot: Now that’s scary.
( Heart beating )
Killua: Never mind. Go!
Illumi: Never over-pursue.
Killua: Go!
( Heart beating )
( Gasping )
But how?
( Thinking )
stop.
How did you know?
Why am I asking that?
Narrator: Meanwhile,
as gon and killua
were fighting for the tiles,
in another part of the ngl...
( Heart beating )
♪
( Heartbeat racing )
( Singing in Japanese )