Gon: I just never thought
that being weak and powerless
could be so frustrating!
♪
Killua: Gon...
for the 30 days
that you can’t use nen...
I’ll protect you.
Whatever it takes,
i’ll keep you safe.
♪
( Singing in Japanese )
Narrator: Colt arrived
carrying a white flag
of surrender
to ask the hunters
for a favor.
His desperate wish was that
they save the dying queen.
After hearing his request,
morel and knov
took Colt to see netero.
Netero: It’s me.
I want you to send over
the chimera ant
research team immediately.
Yes. The king has been born.
contact Dr. Lee
of the fanlin medical college.
have her assemble
a team of the best surgeons
and artificial organ engineering
specialists she can find.
- hmm.
- ( Hangs up )
Be ready to leave here
in four hours.
- Morel: Yes, sir.
- Knov: Yes, sir.
( Both gasp )
Netero: We will do absolutely
everything in our power.
And, Colt...
We’re going to need your help
to accomplish this.
( Colt grunts )
( Netero sighs )
this might just be
the last time I wear this.
Morel: Hey, so is that...
knov: It is,
his "heart" t-shirt.
They say it’s a lucky outfit
that he only wears
when he fights for real.
( Netero breathing deeply )
Knov: I thought
it was just a rumor.
netero: Now then, Colt,
it appears that you can use nen.
Since you’ve been
in the presence
of the new king once before,
your opinion on this matter
would be rather helpful,
so be honest.
How do I compare to the king?
Morel: It really is amazing.
It feels like little needles
stabbing all over my body.
Colt: I doubt...
That you’ll be able
to lay a finger on him.
- Morel: Huh?
- Knov: Hmm?
Colt: You’ll be killed
by one of his royal guards
before you can even get close.
( Netero laughs )
I see.
That’s good to hear.
I’ve found a challenger
at my age.
This is thrilling,
quite thrilling.
( Both gasp )
Netero: Now, morel, the pupils
will be decided today, correct?
- morel: Right.
- Netero: Go with Colt,
and gather the Victors
and research team together.
Then quickly get everyone
over to the nest.
Morel: And you, sir?
You can’t pursue the king alone.
Netero: Oh, no.
i’m off to see
an old friend of mine.
♪
Morel: Don’t forget
my million, okay?
Knov: Oh, you’ll get your money.
Knuckle: What are
you guys talking about?
Morel: Nothing important.
Colt: Let’s go.
Morel: All right.
Bihorn: Everyone else
has already left.
Panda ant: Sure looks that way.
Most of our soldiers
went off and joined
one of the other squads,
except for a handful
of oddballs that defected.
They all decided to stay here.
Colt: We’re fortunate.
I would have expected
some fighting to break out.
( Instruments clattering )
Doctor: Update me.
were you the one
who stopped the bleeding?
Octopus ant: Yes, but i’m afraid
there wasn’t anything else
I could do for her.
Doctor: I’m not sure
we can either.
Don’t expect a miracle.
For the moment,
we’ll attach as many
artificial organs as we can.
Colt: Can you use my organs?
you can have
all of my blood as well.
( Morel gasps )
Doctor: I’m sorry,
but that won’t work.
chimera ants
from different generations
are completely
different organisms.
Just look around you.
You’ll see how much
the chimera ants
in your own generation vary.
( Colt gasps )
Doctor: Thank you, nonetheless.
We promise to do our best.
Let’s just pray that all
these organs keep her alive.
( Monitor beeping )
♪
( Colt groans )
Pray?
damn it.
Is that really all I can do?
- Queen: Someone...
- ( Colt gasps )
Queen: Is anyone there?
colt: Yes!
I’m right by your side.
Is there anything you need?
Morel: What is it?
- Doctor: A signal?
- Octopus ant: Correct.
the queen is
not capable of speech
like the rest of us are.
Doctor: Can you
interpret for me?
She may give us a hint
as to how to save her life.
♪
Queen: Tell me.
My son, how is he?
Is he all right?
Was there anything...
Wrong with him?
Anything at all?
Octopus ant: "Anything at all?"
( Colt gasps )
Don’t worry.
He is perfectly healthy,
and right now--
right now
he’s taken the royal guard
to look for herbs, anything
that might help heal you.
octopus ant:
"...That might help heal you."
( Sighs )
the truth is
that after he killed
and ate
some of the squad leaders,
he left to find
a new territory.
I doubt he will ever return.
Knuckle: Ate them?!
Octopus ant: Yes.
It seems that the king
has no concern for
the queen’s health whatsoever.
Knuckle: Eh?
Queen: Then he’s safe?
The king is safe?
Colt: Yes.
( Queen sighs )
I’m so glad.
( Gasps ) No.
You must send the king
on his journey right away.
( Colt gasps )
Queen: He does not have time
to concern himself
with trifling matters, like me.
He has within him the potential
to rule the entire world.
I was so worried,
because he was born prematurely.
However, it appears...
That I have finally
fulfilled my destiny.
♪
That’s enough for me.
Colt: What are you saying?!
You are our guiding force,
my queen.
Without you, the rest of us will
surely lose our way and perish.
Queen: I know my body
better than anyone else,
and I can say with certainty
I do not have long to live.
Even so, I have no regrets,
not one.
Colt: Please stop!
My queen, you have to live!
Use my body! It’s the only way!
come on!
You have to try, at least!
Doctor: Listen to her.
Respect her wishes.
They may be her last.
( Colt gasps )
Queen: I have one final request.
I-I thought of a name...
For him, for the king.
Colt: A name?
Queen: Meruem.
It means the light
that illuminates all.
( Gasps )
Let...
Him know...
( Colt crying )
Queen: My...
Beloved son.
( Gasps )
( Flatline tone whines )
♪
( Colt gasps )
I failed to protect her again.
I’m useless.
I can’t protect anyone.
( Doctor sighs )
( Knuckle stifling sobs )
Knov: "Again," huh?
Has this happened before?
panda ant:
No, he’s probably referring
to a memory
from when he was human.
- ( Men gasp )
- Morel: Memories?
You have human memories?
panda ant:
Yeah, of course we do,
though some of us remember
better than others.
Our previous human personalities
strongly influence
our behavior now,
but there are many of us
that can still remember
our human names.
if you’ve ever wondered
how we learned to talk so fast,
that’s how.
( Morel sighs )
Colt: Eh?
Huh?
Octopus ant: Hmm?
Colt: What’s that?
( Men gasp )
( Chimera ants gasp )
Octopus ant: Look!
There’s something moving!
Colt: Don’t!
Stand back. I’ll get it myself.
( Octopus ant gasps )
( Chimera ant crying )
Colt: I will protect...
This baby.
I swear it.
I won’t fail, not this time.
( Knuckle stifling sobs )
( Morel clicks tongue )
♪
Knov: Morel?
Morel: Colt, can you promise me
that neither of you
will ever eat a human?
If you can’t make that promise,
then you should get
out of my sight immediately.
But if you’re willing
to give me your word...
I won’t let anyone harm you two,
not as long
as i’m around, anyway.
No enemy gets past me...
And that is a promise.
( Snorts )
♪
( Knuckle laughs )
There’s no doubt about it.
My master has a soft side.
That must be where I got mine!
( Chimera ant crying )
( Gon crying )
( Screams )
Gon: Right! I’m over it now.
Knuckle and the other hunters
are gonna save kite.
I’m sure of it,
so I have to get
a whole lot stronger,
because kite’s coming back,
and I won’t disappoint him.
Spin: So your head’s
on straight after all.
It’s true that you
may have met kite
before we did,
but the fact remains
that we’ve spent much more time
with him than you have.
If you were still moping around
after we’d
crossed the mountains,
I was gonna beat you up.
( Gon gasps )
Spin: Then i’d tell you
kite wouldn’t want to see
you two like this.
i’m positive
that he’s still alive,
and i’m absolutely certain
he wouldn’t want the two of you
to have any regrets.
The question is what to do now.
You should choose wisely
and find the will
to follow through.
If you’re too weak,
then just train more.
There’s enough space in here
for you two
to do some squats and push-ups.
Gon: Yeah. You’re right!
Hey, spin...
Spin: Hmm?
Gon: Why do you
want to be a hunter?
Spin: Because I need the money
so that I can repay
an enormous debt.
have you heard
of the small-billed swan?
Gon: No.
Spin: It’s a species of bird
that only live
around a certain mine.
No one’s been able to figure out
exactly why that is yet.
The food, the water,
the weather,
nothing really explains it.
♪
So we bought the entire area
where the mine is located.
Or rather...
Where what’s left of it is.
Kite financed it for us.
We were just kids who had
nothing to offer in return,
and when we couldn’t find
a single adult
who’d listen to us, he did.
stick and I
both come from that area.
We were born there.
( Swans warbling )
I remember the sight
of thousands
of small-billed swans
taking flight with the light
of dawn at their backs.
it’s the most vivid and
lasting memory stick and I have.
When we found out the area
was slated to become
an industrial waste site,
we finally realized how
important all of it was to us.
Kite told me once
he envied the two of us.
He doesn’t have
a place to call home,
because he doesn’t know
where he was born.
once this mission
is finally over and done with,
i’d really like
to take the two of you there...
To my treasure.
( Footsteps )
( Knuckle and shoot grunt )
( Scraping, fluttering echoing )
♪
Knuckle: Huh?!
Damn. This is...
( Scraping, fluttering )
♪
( Woman gasps )
( Groans )
Cheetu: Finish line!
I truly am the king of speed.
( Slurps )
No one can stop me.
Whoo-hoo!
Alligator ant:
Given cheetu’s speed,
it’s a good bet that he’s
already crossed the border.
Well, I guess I can
take my time searching.
But i’ll find my own paradise
with plenty of food and females.
Cows, pigs, humans,
boars, bears,
i don’t even care,
as long as they’re plentiful.
Because i’m the king,
the king of eaters.
Narrator: The chimera ants
that were once soldiers
have now departed in order
to become kings themselves.
Meanwhile the king himself
is now in the Republic
of east gorteau.
King: Hmm.
♪
( Singing in Japanese )