Neferpitou: Someone is out there
running around
and disabling my puppets.
Can you go and kill them?
Leol: Yes, you can count on me.
Killua: Hah!
Yeah, bring it on,
tanks, jets, whatever
the hell else you’ve got.
I’ll take all of ’em down.
♪
( Singing in Japanese )
Narrator: Knuckle and shoot are
on the move to capture cheetu
as he attempts
to return to the king.
( Brush rustles )
Knuckle: He’s close.
Shoot: Very well.
Knuckle: He’s still on the road.
If he stays the course,
he’ll pass by here
in ten minutes.
Shoot: Do you really think
he’ll stick to the road?
knuckle: No.
He’ll notice my presence
just before he gets here,
because a.P.R. Will start
accruing interest again.
However, given his high speed...
We may be able to attack him
just before
the next interest announcement.
Narrator: Chapter 7 bankruptcy
announces accumulated interest
every ten seconds,
and a.P.R. Informs the enemy
interest will be accrued,
but the count is interrupted
if the target gets more than
100 meters away from knuckle.
The remaining time
is then stored,
saved in a.P.R.’s memory,
and then as soon as the target
gets within a 100-meter radius
of knuckle once again,
the count picks up
exactly where it left off.
Knuckle: He’s approaching at
a speed between 160 to 180 kph.
If there are still
three seconds or more
before a.P.R.
Adds interest again,
there’s a chance we can attack
before he notices us.
- ( Shoot gasps )
- Knuckle: Get ready.
♪
( Shoot shuddering )
( Knuckle growls )
Eh?
Shoot: What’s wrong?
Knuckle: Damn it.
What just happened?
He changed direction
at the last second!
- Shoot: Huh?
- Knuckle: There!
- Shoot: Calm down.
- ( Knuckle growls )
Shoot: It’s not worth it.
He has the speed of a cheetah.
We’ll never catch up.
Knuckle: He’s not supposed
to know how to deal with zetsu.
How the hell did he
discover our ambush?
Wait.
A slight breeze...
But we’re downwind,
so he didn’t smell us.
- Shoot: Look up.
- Knuckle: Huh?
What the hell is that?
♪
flutter: I’ve found
two suspicious figures. Advise.
Leol: Ignore them.
They aren’t the target.
There’s no point
in doing more work
than absolutely necessary.
Flutter: Right.
it appears
that they were attempting
to ambush sir cheetu.
Leol: Oh. So he’s in the area?
Flutter: I warned sir cheetu
before he ran into their trap.
Was that unnecessary?
Leol: What did he do?
Flutter: He took a detour
toward the capital.
He told me that I should
thank you for the help.
Leol: I see. Good work.
He owes me one now.
( Cellphone rings )
Leol here.
neferpitou: The target
just engaged a squad of soldiers
in the city of luonton.
Leol: Luonton?
Neferpitou: Start preparing
an ambush to the north of them.
I just have a little hunch.
Leol: On it.
menthuthuyoupi: Guess
the military can’t handle it.
Neferpitou: No. But they’re
only there to buy time, anyway.
They’ve had to stay
in one particular area
for longer than expected, meow.
We should all bear in mind
that they have been
constantly on the move
for more than 30 hours straight.
♪
Killua: Diego’s fallen
into enemy hands!
If you stay in your homes,
you’ll be killed!
Man: Liar!
Man #2: Rebel scum!
Killua: Crap.
Diego just appeared
on television
to show he’s alive and well.
The odds are against me now.
So much for inciting riots.
I’ve gotta take out
as many puppets
and soldiers as I can.
( Panting )
Well, should I try
heading north?
gon: I knew it.
Someone’s still following me.
who’s there?!
Come out, and show yourself!
( Footsteps stop )
The presence is gone.
It might just be following me
until more ants show up.
I’ll shake them off.
we’ll see
who has greater endurance.
Leol: Hey.
Cheetu: Hey.
Leol: Sorry that I
had to stop you.
Cheetu: Nah. I was
already headed this way.
is the king
this direction, hagya?
( Leol growls )
Cheetu: Yeah, I know.
It’s leol now.
Leol: Not a slip of the tongue?
You’re still a bastard.
you know that?
Cheetu: Flutter’s warning
was a really big help to me.
i’m trying to avoid
getting into fights right now.
leol: Glad to hear it.
By the way, what’s that thing?
Cheetu: Hmm? Don’t know.
A hunter hit me with it
a little while ago.
It just follows me
wherever I run to.
I guess i’m stuck with it,
but so far, it doesn’t seem
to have any effect on me.
- Leol: Should I get rid of it?
- Cheetu: Hmm?
Leol: I said, you want it gone?
Cheetu: You can do that?
Leol: Probably.
Cheetu: But it’ll cost me?
( Leol chuckles )
I’m glad that you’re
a smart guy.
Cheetu: I thought as much.
Leol: The royal guard
has assigned me a mission.
I’d like your help on it.
Flutter: Sir leol.
Leol: Hmm?
flutter:
I’ve spotted the target.
He’s headed north on the road
through the forest
northeast of luonton.
leol: It seems
that lord neferpitou’s hunch
was right on the money.
Don’t let him escape.
slow him down
by any means necessary.
Flutter: Right.
Leol: We’re trying
to chase down a human,
probably a hunter.
Cheetu: And you want me
to help hunt him?
You said he’s a hunter?
They can be pretty difficult
to deal with.
Leol: I know.
I’ve planned ahead.
Cheetu: ’kay.
Leol: Lord shaiapouf
has prepared a power
that’s custom-tailored for you.
He’ll instruct you
on how you’re to use it.
with any luck,
you can master it in a day.
I’m a slow learner,
so mine took me three days
to get the hang of.
Cheetu: All right.
Sounds like a sweet deal.
I swear loyalty to the king
in return?
( Leol chuckles )
exactly.
Easy enough, right?
Cheetu: When you
put it like that, sure.
( Leol laughs )
You really are sharp.
If you accept,
return to the castle,
master your new power,
and then contact me.
In the meantime,
i’ll have my underlings
determine the prey’s abilities.
cheetu: Yeah,
I guess I owe you one.
Might as well.
Anyway...
You’re still all about
stealing glory, aren’t you?
( Leol laughs )
Well, naturally.
I used to be king of the jungle,
you know.
Cheetu: Sounds like you’re
looking to reclaim your throne.
Killua: Damn it.
I’m being followed.
And he’s way out of yo-yo range.
If I don’t lose him or beat him,
i’m in trouble.
- Hey, there’s a jungle!
- flutter: Eh?
Killua: The canopy leaves
are dense enough
that he shouldn’t be able
to see me from the air,
and if he comes down here,
he’ll be in range of my yo-yo.
( Killua panting )
Looks like he’s not coming.
Did I lose him already?
If I did, he’s bound
to come looking for me.
Damn.
I don’t have time
to wait around.
Come on. Hurry up.
( Flutter chuckles )
you can run,
but you can’t hide from me.
Now go forth, leol army!
Go and capture our prey!
♪
Killua: Something’s coming
from the opposite side,
and it’s on the ground.
( Gasps )
( Beetle ant laughs )
Huh?
He took his foe’s hands
and arms with one swing!
We don’t stand a chance
one-on-one.
Where is he?
Chimera ant:
Captain, above you!
Beetle ant: Huh?!
- Monkey ant: Aha!
- ( Chimera ants yell )
( Neck cracks )
- Monkey ant: No!
- ( Killua yelps )
I missed two of ’em.
beetle ant:
Trying to gang up on him
in the treetops
isn’t working at all.
Retreat! Time to regroup!
Killua: Oh, no, you don’t.
You must be the leader.
I’ll take you out first!
( Beetle ant laughing )
Well, what do you say, kid?
How’d you like that blast?
Killua: That bastard.
He just farted at me!
No, there’s a bigger problem.
I completely concealed
my presence
and attacked
from his blind spot,
but he countered
at the perfect time.
someone must be
feeding him information.
It’s him.
He’s probably
watching right now.
I’d guess he’s got a power that
lets him pinpoint my location.
In that case...
♪
I can’t show my hand just yet.
I don’t want them to know about
my electro-shocks or my yo-yo.
I’d like to shake them off
and go back to hiding,
but that won’t work.
i’ll have
to beat them all without...
( Groans )
A gun?
No. There’s something
stuck to my face.
( Flea chatters )
Killua: A flea?
Hatters )
( Yelps )
Damn it!
Where is it coming from?
♪
Flutter: Area th-88,
x-15, y-12, z-2.
Point x-9, y-3, z-1.
( Beeping )
Chimera ant: Okay.
( Wind blowing )
( Humming a tune )
♪ There’s no escaping
♪ no, there’s not
♪ not from my fleadom
- ♪ oh, yeah
- ( Fluid rushing )
( Rifle fires )
( Killua grunts )
( Flea chatters )
Killua: Damn it!
My temple won’t stop bleeding.
These fleas aren’t just big.
Flutter: Area p.Q.,
y-7, x-8, z-4.
Point y-5, x-3, z-1.
Sniper: Okay.
( Inhales )
( Killua yelps )
the sniper’s
not going for serious damage.
I guess he figures
the more blood I lose,
the more i’ll
exhaust my strength.
( Sniper humming )
♪ My fleas are so special
♪ so very, very special
they have
a 200-meter vertical leap.
♪ And when you factor in
( inhales )
♪ The power of my air gun
♪ then they become unstoppable
♪ oh, yeah
flutter: He’s already
able to dodge them?
It’s no wonder those apes
weren’t able to do anything.
Killua: If I keep
running around,
it’ll be harder
for them to snipe me,
but i’ve gotta be careful
and conserve my energy.
♪
flutter: Ah.
He’s going to try something.
He may try to use his ability.
Sniper: Yeah.
Flutter: Let’s see
what he can do.
Sniper: Okay.
( Inhales )
flutter: My super eye
allows me to observe a target
from multiple angles
via my satellite dragonflies.
Nothing you can do
can escape my sight.
So come on. Do something!
♪
Narrator: Killua cannot use en.
He was not adept
at the skills required
to expand his aura around him
and maintain it for a long time.
Killua knows this and keeps his
aura within a manageable range,
just 57 centimeters
from his body.
therefore,
as soon as a projectile
is within that range,
killua must rely
on his incredible reflexes
as well as his strength
to react with desperate speed
and dodge the enemy’s attack
at point-blank range.
The margin of error
is unfortunately
all but nonexistent.
But this time,
he did not dodge it.
This way, he could determine
the bullet’s trajectory.
( Killua grunts )
Damn it.
It came from this way!
♪
flutter: Ah.
He allowed himself to be hit
so he could locate the sniper.
The target is heading your way,
and quickly!
Sniper: Okay.
♪ this is all
within expected parameters ♪
Killua: The bleeding’s
completely stopped
where the fleas only grazed me.
I’m betting those things
must secrete some kind
of special anticoagulant.
i can’t afford
any more bleeding wounds,
but I won’t let him get away!
Gon: This is the perfect spot.
I have a clear view
in all directions.
You like that?!
now there’s
nowhere for you to hide,
so come on out!
Meleoron: Wait!
The desert is massive.
If you don’t have any water,
you’ll die of thirst in a day.
( Gon grunts )
- ( Footsteps )
- ( Gasps )
Meleoron: Aw, man.
I wanted to observe you
a little longer,
but I guess that won’t work.
I was running low
on stamina, anyway.
I suppose this gives us
more time to talk things over.
First, introductions.
Hello. My name is jail--
uh, I mean call me meleoron.
I was a squadron leader
when the queen was alive.
Nice to meet you.
And what’s your name?
Gon: Why were you following me?
Meleoron: Because I didn’t
want you getting away,
and I sure couldn’t
just let you die,
because you’ll make
a really valuable partner.
Do you have business
with the king?
Gon: I don’t.
Meleoron: Huh?
( Gon gasps )
I almost let it slip.
he approached me
with an ulterior motive.
I can’t tell him
anything else.
Meleoron: Really?
I thought that you guys
were here to defeat the king.
- Gon: "You guys"?
- ( Meleoron gasps )
( Laughs )
Yeah, that’s right.
I’ve actually been watching you
ever since that other kid
was with you.
Gon: I get it now.
( Meleoron gasps )
Gon: And you picked me
over killua.
thought i’d put up
less of a fight, didn’t you?
Meleoron: Huh? Wait!
You’ve got it all wrong!
Is that how it sounded?
Okay, that makes sense.
I mean, I know what I look like.
You think i’m an enemy.
Guess I should have been
more clear about that.
Listen, I swear i’m not lying!
I’m not looking to trick
or defeat you, okay? Promise.
Gon: Okay. I believe you.
Meleoron: I get it.
It’s a lot to take in.
Believe me. I mean, if I were
in your shoes, I wouldn’t--
( gasps ) Huh?
Killua: Is that him?
♪
Sniper: ♪ it’s a trap
♪ come on in if you wanna
( neck cracks )
Killua: I don’t care. Die.
chimera ant:
He went for the kill
instantly and
without hesitation.
I’m impressed.
( Gags )
♪
Killua: A lake?
Octopus ant: Want to see hell?
Well, here you go!
- Fish ant: Blood!
- Fish ant #2: Food!
Fish ant #1: It’s food!
Fish ant #2: Wait! This is--
it’s captain ikalgo’s host!
fish ant #1:
Stop eating it, damn it!
fish ant #2: Look,
I want to stop, but I can’t!
fish ant #1:
The blood is calling us!
Can’t you hear it?!
Ikalgo: You--you little bastard!
How dare you chop off the great
ikalgo’s precious arms!
killua: Sorry,
but I couldn’t exactly
let you drag me
into the water.
Wait. "Ika" means squid,
and you’re an octopus,
aren’t you?
ikalgo:
Don’t call me an octopus!
♪
narrator:
Killua’s opponent is ikalgo,
a chimera ant
resembling an octopus
that uses human hosts.
ikalgo:
Don’t call me an octopus!
( Singing in Japanese )