Kite: Have a bad feeling.
It’s like i’m missing something.
♪
There’s a gnawing anxiety
that won’t go away.
♪
( Singing in Japanese )
Narrator: Kite, gon, and killua
have taken care
of hagya’s subordinates.
Now they continue
their harrowing journey,
and as they head
deeper and deeper
into the heart of the ngl,
hoping beyond hope
to finally locate
the chimera ants’ nest
within the queen’s castle,
they are completely unaware
that one of the king’s three
royal guards is about to awaken.
( Fluid sloshes )
( Hagya scoffs )
It’s magic.
I just wonder
what kind of magic they use.
Hina: Oh, my gosh!
They were
all split right in half!
Flutter: It is quite impressive.
By the look of this one,
he was crushed by a rock
or some other hard object.
Hagya: Surprising, since baro’s
the one with an iron shell.
So this is what rares
are capable of.
Hina:
Are you getting worried now?
Hagya: Come on. I have
the king of the jungle’s blood
flowing in my veins.
It’ll take more
than a few humans to scare me.
Hina:
You’ve got a point there.
( Sighs ) That’s a relief.
I was starting to think
I was going to have to miss out
on the yummy feast tonight.
Hagya: These must be
extremely rare humans indeed.
We’ll tear them limb from limb,
and then we’ll fill up
our bellies with their flesh!
♪
Kite: We’re being followed.
( Boys gasp )
Kite: Not from there.
There are quite a few of them.
( Wings buzzing )
Flutter: Listen up.
Your primary objective
is to distract the enemy
while attacking
from a safe distance.
Don’t get too close.
The second platoon
will take the right
while the third platoon
pincers them from the left.
My first platoon will trap them,
preventing retreat to the rear.
Now go!
♪
Killua: Gon and I didn’t even
notice they were here.
Kite: They’re coming
from the left and right.
Keep your guard up.
( Wings buzzing )
Killua: Ah, damn it!
Gon: The trees
are getting in the way!
Killua: Yeah, I know.
Gon: Shouldn’t we
get out of the forest?
Kite: I think it’s a trap.
Flutter: Good.
Keep up the chase.
Lord hagya, everything is
going according to plan.
( Both laugh )
Hagya: Nice work, flutter.
( Growls )
( Hina gasps )
Hagya: As soon as the platoons
drive our prey into range,
one strike from my fangs
will finish them off.
Hina: Yeah, okay, but
something doesn’t feel right.
- Hagya: Eh?
- Hina: Well,
you ordered flutter
to chase down the prey
while you hid in the grass
to ambush them.
That’s pretty lame,
don’t you think?
- Hagya: Huh?
- Hina: I mean,
aren’t you
the king of the jungle?
A king should face his prey,
not hide.
You should just jump
right out at them
and go "chomp chomp! Rooowr!"
And then you laugh all evil.
That’d be a whole lot cooler.
Am I right?
Hagya: You forget that this is
how the king of the jungle hunts
in the animal kingdom,
so shut up, and watch!
Hina: Yeah, yeah.
I guess it doesn’t matter much
either way as long
as I still get to eat the rares.
( Meat squishing )
Pig ant: A rare, huh?
What the hell is that?
Peggy: I’ll explain
the details later.
Its number is
four-dash-nine-three-three.
It was caught and brought in
by zazan’s squad.
Pig ant:
Four-dash-nine-three-three?
Sorry. Doesn’t ring a bell,
but it’s probably been offered
to the queen already.
Thing is her appetite
has been getting
much more ravenous lately.
She’s gonna give birth
to an incredible king.
Don’t see it. Must already be
inside the queen’s belly.
Peggy: Are you sure?
Pig ant: Well, it isn’t here,
and I can’t think of any
other place that it would be.
Peggy: Is it possible
it escaped?
Rammot: Creatures that have
been injected with our venom
are rendered immobile
for well over a month,
so there’s no way
it could move freely
in just three short days.
Peggy: You can’t be certain
when it concerns the rares.
They definitely aren’t like
the humans we’re familiar with,
and I would have thought
that you, of all people,
would be aware of that.
Rammot: Well,
i’m not the same creature
that I was before.
I’ll see them again,
and when I do,
I swear i’m going
to rip them apart,
crush them, and eat them.
♪
Pokkle: The antidote I hid
in my molar came in handy,
but I can barely drag myself
across the ground.
Probably best to just lay low
here for the time being.
Still, what the hell’s going on?
How can a chimera ant use nen?
Peggy: Would you mind
checking once more?
Pig ant: Come on.
Cut me a little slack.
I’m already drowning
in a bunch of work as it is.
Didn’t you hear
what I just said?
The queen has
a huge appetite right now.
Peggy: Yes, I heard you,
and I am fully aware of that.
Pig ant: I don’t know anything
about all this "rare" stuff,
but why are you
so obsessed with this human?
Peggy: I’d like to ask it
some questions.
Look at rammot.
Can’t you see the light
that’s surrounding his body?
Pig ant: A light, huh?
No, I don’t see anything.
Peggy: I see. Then it’s true
that not everyone is able
to identify this power.
Rammot: That means
that it’s a gift.
Mm, yes.
This gift is my destiny
bestowed upon by the heavens,
the power of a chosen few.
If I can just figure out
how to master this power,
I can become the king,
and I will rule!
( Chorus vocalizing )
Flutter: Retreat! Retreat!
Both: Hmm?
Hagya: What’s wrong, flutter?
- ( Rumble )
- ( Both gasp )
( Chorus vocalizing )
Hagya: Wait. What is that?
( Hina yelps )
( Footsteps )
( Hagya gasping )
( Hina squeals )
He’s so handsome!
Hagya: We’re heading back
right now.
Hina: Eh? But the feast!
( Hagya sighs )
( Growls )
Kite: He must have understood
that he was
completely outclassed
and backed down
calmly and immediately,
so he’s more than likely
a squadron leader.
♪
Hagya: My fangs and my claws...
I used to think
they were the center
of the entire universe.
All I had to do
was brandish them,
and in a blink of an eye,
I could end a creature’s life
and satisfy my hunger.
There was
no greater bliss than that.
However, that wasn’t the case.
There was always
someone greater,
and I didn’t stand
at the top of the food chain.
I learned this
at the cost of my life,
but it made me even stronger.
♪
As we are now, we have
no chance of defeating them.
But we’ve gained a new weapon,
the ability to learn.
Kite: We’re going
to follow them.
( Boys gasp )
Kite: Their nest
must be close to here,
so wherever they’re going,
the queen is bound to be there.
♪
( Rammot gasping )
( Peggy gasps )
What is that?
Some--something
is coming our way.
( Rammot gasps )
Royal guard: That was
an interesting story.
You mentioned
something about gifts?
Do you mind...
If I join you?
( Rammot gasping )
That’s o-one of the queen’s
elite royal guards!
If I can just figure out
how to master this power,
I can become the king,
and I will rule!
It was a dream,
a brief and foolish one at that.
( Royal guard chuckles )
♪
Rammot: They’re on
a whole different level...
A predestined status,
one that cannot be altered!
( Gasping )
Royal guard:
It’s okay. Just relax.
Let’s go talk over there.
( Rammot gasps )
Y-yes, sir!
My power does not exist
for my benefit.
It is for me to be
of service to them
as well as the king they serve!
My power is for serving them!
♪
( Pokkle shudders )
Impossible!
What is this aura?
It--it’s so ominous.
Royal guard:
Oh, and by the way...
Rammot: Huh?
Royal guard:
Why is there a live human
hiding underneath
that pile of bones?
( Pokkle gasps )
Peggy: Ah...
( Heart beating )
( Pokkle gasping )
( Rammot growls )
Royal guard: Mm. Meow I get it.
Peggy: May I ask
what you’re researching?
Royal guard: I’m reading
about those rares
you mentioned earlier.
Peggy: I have attempted
to study them many times myself,
but little
is written about them.
Royal guard:
Asking one of them is faster
than flipping
through some dusty, old books.
That’s why you were
looking for one of them
in the first place.
Isn’t that right?
Peggy: Yes, that was indeed
the cause of our search.
Royal guard: Oh, here we go.
Yes, right here. Let’s see.
"New memories are stored
in the hippocampus,
"while old memories are kept
in the cerebral cortex.
In order to invoke
those memories"...
Hmm. Meow I get it.
( Peggy grunts )
Royal guard:
You, come over here.
( Chuckles )
♪
Pokkle: Hatsu is a technique
for manipulating aura at will.
To summarize the categories
of nen users, they are...
Enhancers...
Transmuters...
Conjurers...
Emitters...
Manipulators...
And lastly specialists,
for a total of six categories.
C-categories.
Royal guard: Meow. Meow.
( Squishing )
Pokkle: Every nen user belongs
to one of these subtypes.
( Royal guard grunts )
Pokkle: You want--
you want to increase
the amount of your aura
as well as the speed
of its flow.
Basic training is spent
on increasing the amount of aura
and quickening its flow,
and the outcomes of battle
using nen abilities
are--are swayed
significantly by--
by--
( squishing )
By--by these--
these two s-skills.
Royal guard: Meow I see.
Pokkle: Besides
the basics of nen,
such as zetsu and ren,
an individual’s abilit--
an individual’s abilities are...
Deeply influenced by his own--
his own idiosyncrasies.
If your subtype and preference
are luckily the same...
Your ability
may be more powerful.
Royal guard: Hmm.
Tell me, how do you identify
which nen subtype you belong to?
( Squishing )
Pokkle: Water divination is--
is the simplest
and most commonly used method
to identify...
Royal guard: Water divination?
Go ahead, rammot.
Give it a try.
Rammot: Yes, sir.
♪
( Rammot gasps )
( Peggy gasps )
Royal guard:
The water is overflowing,
so that must make you
an enhancer, huh?
Rammot: An enhancer?
Peggy: More importantly,
it confirms
that rammot is a nen user.
Isn’t that right?
Royal guard: It seems so.
Oh, yeah.
Didn’t you say that you
fought with a rare
before all this happened?
Rammot: Yes. I did.
Royal guard: I think the impact
from its attacks
must have opened up
your aura nodes.
That, in turn,
released your aura.
Rammot: Nodes?
Royal guard: Apparently
they’re small holes
all over your body.
It seems that if they’re sealed,
your aura can’t be released.
Peggy: I see. In fact,
Colt presented the same theory
not long ago,
that rammot’s change
was triggered
by his fight with the rares.
It would appear
that he was correct.
So then, if rammot has
indeed become a nen user,
do you think we can use him
to open everyone’s nodes?
Royal guard:
Yes, I believe that we can.
Hmph.
Now i’d like
to give this a try.
( Nen flowing )
( Both gasp )
( Royal guard laughs )
The leaf withered away.
Peggy: Impossible.
One of us was actually born
possessing nen ability
without having to fight
a rare to obtain it.
Forgive me, commander,
but that makes you
a specialist, correct?
It means you don’t belong
to any of the other categories?
Royal guard: It’s neferpitou.
- Rammot: Huh?
- Peggy: Eh?
Neferpitou: That is the name
the queen bestowed upon me.
From now on,
you can call me neferpitou.
Both: Yes, sir!
Neferpitou:
I don’t need that anymore.
Go and feed him to the queen.
Both: Of course!
( Neferpitou humming )
♪
Narrator: Even from birth,
neferpitou already possessed
incredible power.
This revelation, while
celebrated by the chimera ants,
casts a dark shadow
over the fates of gon
and his friends.
♪
( Singing in Japanese )