( Fanfare plays )
Zepile: Hey, that’s your target
right over there...
The tycoon, Mr. Battera.
( Cameras whirring )
Battera: What am I watching?
Well, the "greed island"
video game, of course.
Reporter: But what
makes you so interested
in a video game, sir?
You’ve spent a considerable
amount of money on it already.
Battera: The answer,
my dear, is love.
When you fall in love
with something,
you want it all to yourself.
Reporter: Love? Really?
There are so many rumors
flying around.
Would you like
to make a comment?
Gon: I’m gonna get my hands
on the clue ging left.
♪
( Singing in Japanese )
Kurapika: What...Time is it?
( Both gasp )
Leorio: Kurapika!
Melody: It’s 2:00 P.M.
( Kurapika sighs )
So I slept for a half a day?
Leorio: Well,
more like two days, buddy.
Kurapika: Where’s the boss?
And what about the auction?
Melody: Oh, uh,
they canceled it completely.
The rest of the merchandise
will be sold online.
The boss accepted that.
Kurapika: Don’t lie to me.
( Melody gasps )
Kurapika: The boss
was really looking forward
to taking part in the auction.
I don’t see her
accepting that so easily.
♪
Melody: The troupe
murdered squala.
( Kurapika gasps )
Melody: And Eliza,
well, she was inconsolable.
The Scarlet eyes we won
were stolen,
but apparently the boss was
more upset over eliza’s state
than the loss
of her prized possession.
That was when she informed us
she wanted to go home.
Kurapika: I understand.
Gon and killua?
Melody: They’re both just fine,
and right now--
- leorio: He’s out.
- ( Water splashes )
Rest up.
Your friends
are doing what they have to,
so you don’t have to worry
about a thing, okay?
Emcee: Our next item
is the fabled game...
Known as "greed island."
( Crowd murmurs )
( Gasping )
♪
Emcee: And it has
a mysterious power.
- ( Footsteps thudding )
- Let’s take a look.
( Crowd gasps )
( Gasping )
Emcee: Now, as i’m sure
all of you can plainly see,
a mysterious power protects
the console from any damage.
Well, as long as someone
is playing inside the game,
that is.
This man is jeitsari.
He’s the player who’s inside
the game even as we speak.
As a matter of fact, he’s
the one who signed a contract
allowing us to auction it off.
Gon: So ging didn’t
bring this one here.
Emcee: Jeitsari left behind
the following contract
that stipulates,
if no one has cleared the game
by the contract date,
even if he
and the seven other players
are still inside the game,
he would consign
all seven units of the game
as well as the consoles
to the southernpiece auction
and entrust his dream
of clearing the game
to other challengers.
Unfortunately,
when we received these units,
the game had ended
for two players.
Losing the game results
in actual death for a player.
This dangerous game requires
that you risk your own life.
Only bid if you’re prepared
for the consequences.
The starting bid
is 900 million Jenny!
( Overlapping bids )
Emcee: I have one billion.
1.5.
Number 105 doubles it.
71 doubles again to six billion.
( Milluki growls )
Killua: Crap, my big brother.
Gon: So you use your hand
to tell her
how much you want to bid?
Zepile: Yeah. The auctioneer
looks at the crowd’s
hand signals
to discern
the highest bid instantly.
Emcee: Number 16
doubles it again to 12 billion!
Gon: What’s this mean?
Emcee: 201 doubles it again
to 24 billion!
Zepile: You idiot!
( Battera scoffs )
Emcee: Number 16
bids 25 billion.
( Both sigh )
Gon: That was a close one.
Killua: Okay, so i’m guessing
he wasn’t able to decipher
that memory card.
( Milluki groans )
Emcee: I have 25.5 billion.
Killua: How much money
does he have?
( Battera chuckles )
Emcee: Number 16
raises to 30.5 billion!
( Crowd gasping )
( Milluki groans )
( Man exhales )
30 and a half. Is that right?
Battera: It’s of no consequence.
Or at least it won’t be,
as long as we’re able
to clear the game.
Gon: Excuse us,
but the two of us are hunters.
Killua: We’re willing
to offer our help
in clearing "greed island."
Bodyguard: That’s real funny.
Now why don’t you two run along?
Gon: We’re not joking.
I really am
a professional hunter.
Bodyguard: Sure you are.
Battera: I assume
you have a hunter’s license.
Gon: Yes, sir.
Killua: It’s at the pawnshop,
remember?
Gon: Eh, I don’t have it on me.
Bodyguard #2: What a surprise.
- I knew he was lying.
- Gon: No, i’m not!
Battera: Just hold on a moment.
The fact you’re here
at the auction
in the first place
tells me
you’re no ordinary children.
However, I can’t take your word
at face value.
I am looking to hire
professional hunters
in order to clear this game.
That much is true,
but i’m afraid I simply can’t
hire either of you at this time.
Because there’s a limit to
the number of players, you see.
Killua: Not good.
Did we fail already?
Gon: I’m thinking we don’t
actually need to buy the game,
not if we just want
the data inside it,
and I bet there are
probably gonna be
some people
who win "greed island,"
who are gonna look for other
people to play it for them.
( Killua gasps )
Gon: The number of players
is limited?
Battera: Each memory card
only has the capacity
to store one player’s data.
With multitaps,
you can have a maximum
of eight players per console.
Gon: Hey, he’s right.
Remember?
That "greed island" save
used up all 30 blocks
on that memory card.
Killua: Yeah.
Battera: How did you know?
Gon: We got a "greed island"
save file a little while back,
so we figured it out.
Battera: What about
the game itself?
Have you played it?
Gon: No. We only have
a memory card.
( Battera thinking )
Wait. Does that mean...
If the memory card
you speak of is real,
you would still need
another item
in order to remove the card
from the console.
( Gon gasps ) You think maybe...
Killua: He means the ring.
( Battera thinking )
They know about the ring, too?
It appears that these two boys
may be worthy
of our consideration.
Man: I assume you know nen.
Let’s have a demonstration
of your ren.
( Both gasp ) Okay!
Battera: What do you think?
Man: Hopeless, i’m afraid.
Hiring them would be
a complete waste.
They would simply run around
in circles until they died.
♪
Gon: How do you know
when we haven’t even tried?
Man: It’d be too late by then.
You see, better to die quick
than squeak by.
You would only be delaying
the inevitable.
See, as long as a player
is alive inside the game,
you can’t reset, nor can
you remove the memory card.
In other words, it’s impossible
to send in new players.
Battera: I’ve personally hired
around 100 professional
and amateur hunters
to play this game,
and just over half of them
have already given up.
Gon: What do you mean?
Battera: They’ve given up
on ever returning
to the real world,
choosing instead to live
their lives inside the game.
That’s why i’m so careful
selecting players.
We need people strong enough
to obtain items
and then return them safely
to the real world,
so of course we have to be
much more selective.
Gon: Are you trying to imply
that we’re not strong enough?
Killua: Yeah! Why does that guy
think we can’t do it?!
Battera: Because he is
a professional hunter
and one who has played
"greed island" before.
( Both gasp )
Hunter: Speaking from my own
ample experience,
the items we wish to bring here
are easy to obtain.
With your paltry nen,
it’s hopeless.
As a matter of fact,
it’d be game over for you
in no time.
Once the screening is complete,
i’ll be returning to the game.
Killua: Wait.
You’re gonna be screening
players while you’re here?
Hunter: That’s right, starting
on the final day of the auction.
So if you’re planning
to participate,
I would recommend putting some
additional work into your nen.
Gon: We were
gonna do that anyway!
Come on. Let’s go.
Hunter: Before you leave,
how did you come to have
a memory card?
Gon: I’m not telling!
( Hunter chuckles )
( Door slams )
Killua: Damn it! Those jerks.
Gon: We definitely
gotta pass their screening now.
Phinks: Screening, huh?
So what’s the plan?
Feitan: Do you even need to ask?
( Explosion )
Feitan: We are bandits.
We steal, of course.
Phinks: Well, let’s go back
to the hideout and play it.
Phinks: A memory card
is already inserted,
which means
only one more person can play.
We’ll use a multitap.
Four more can play now.
Phinks: Very nice.
So who’s gonna go in first?
Feitan: I will.
♪
( Phinks gasps )
He’s really gone.
I didn’t think
that would actually happen.
Machi: What was that?
Phinks: It’s a game.
You guys wanna play?
Machi: I pass.
Franklin: Maybe a little later.
Phinks: Fine.
I’ll catch you later, then.
( All gasp )
Shizuku: He disappeared, too.
Machi: It’s a game, right?
What kind?
Franklin: It says right here
that it’s one
where you can actually die.
It’s listed in the catalog
for the auction.
Shalnark: Hmm.
( Gon yells )
I can’t believe he treated us
like we’re just dirt!
Damn it!
Killua: I know, but you’ve gotta
admit that he’s got a point.
Gon: What do you mean?
Killua: Just chill out a little.
Look, we should start thinking
about taking all this
to the next level.
Gon: What are you talking about?
Killua: Hatsu.
I mean our special attacks.
Gon: Huh?
Killua: Think about it.
Kurapika started learning nen
the same time we did,
and because
of his special attack,
he was able to take on
the phantom troupe.
♪
Gon: Yeah, with the powers
that he obtained,
he basically became
invincible against them
by placing his life on the line.
Killua: We can’t
limit ourselves.
( Gon grunts )
Killua: We need special attacks
that fit our specialties
and that can minimize the risk,
something practical
and effective.
That’s what we need
to come up with.
( Music slows, stops )
Gon: Hmm.
( Killua groans )
I figured this would happen.
Let’s take one step at a time.
First off, what kind of
abilities do you want to have?
Gon: That’s a good question.
Well...
( Killua groans ) Hey!
You must have an idea
at least, don’t you?
Gon: Uh, a really strong one.
Killua: Be more specific, man.
To start with,
think about something
that’s in your own category.
You’re an enhancer, right?
Try to think of a power
that enhances something.
Gon: ’kay.
Killua: Then think about
what part you want to strengthen
and exactly how
you want to do it.
Gon: Hey, that hurt!
What ability do you want, then?
Killua: I already know,
and that’s why i’m trying
to help you out right now.
Gon: Really? What is it?
Killua: It’s a secret.
Gon: Aww.
Killua: Gon,
i’m gonna go practice
my special attack now,
and you keep thinking
about yours, okay?
If you don’t,
I might be the only one
who passes the screening.
- ( Door closes )
- ( Gon sighs )
Killua: If I don’t put
a little fear in him,
chances are he’s only
gonna get distracted.
( Nen whooshing )
Visualize my aura...
Infused with electricity.
( Grunting )
Then visualize discharging
the stored electricity
while refining my nen.
Hunter: With your paltry nen,
it’d be game over for you
in no time.
Gon: Damn that guy!
I’ll show him game over!
Kurapika: I see
you’re hard at work.
Gon: Kurapika!
You feeling any better?
Yeah. My fever broke,
so i’m all right now.
Gon: Wow.
He sure doesn’t look all right.
But if kurapika finds out
that the spiders
are still in yorknew city,
will there be
any way to stop him?
Kurapika: Tell me,
how did everything go
at the auction?
I believe you were going
after an expensive game.
Gon: Uh, yeah.
Kurapika: I see.
So they’re screening players,
are they?
Gon: Hey, what kind of training
did you do while you were gone?
Kurapika: Once I decided
I wanted to conjure chains,
mostly imagery training.
Not only did I feel them
with my eyes closed,
I drew hundreds,
maybe thousands of sketches.
I looked at chains
and even tasted them,
smelled, and listened.
My master told me
to play with them constantly,
so that’s exactly what I did.
After a while,
he took them away from me,
and it was then that I began
to hallucinate chains.
It wasn’t long after that
the hallucinations felt heavy,
I could feel them,
cold and grating,
and once that happened,
I was able
to conjure chains myself.
But otherwise,
it was the same as you,
just ten and ren.
Gon: ’kay.
( Gasps )
I’ve got an idea.
You can be my master.
You can point out
what i’m doing right
and what i’ve got wrong.
This way, I can keep kurapika
busy while the auction happens.
Kurapika: I’m sorry,
but I can’t.
- Gon: What?
- Kurapika: I’m afraid
that my boss
will be leaving tomorrow,
and i’m obligated
to accompany her.
Gon: You’re leaving yorknew?
Kurapika: Yes,
although i’m still concerned
about the spiders.
But it has been two days now,
so I suppose
they probably left already.
( Gon sighs ) Well,
it’s probably for the best.
Kurapika: But what about you?
Who taught you nen?
You should ask them.
They’d be a better resource
than I am.
( Wing laughs )
A special attack?
That’s just like you two.
I can tell you this much.
Enhancers really don’t need
a special attack at all.
Gon: But why not?
Wing: Well, because enhancers
are the most balanced,
both in offense and defense.
If you can master ten and ren,
you will produce enough force
to be quite destructive indeed.
Gon: What if I don’t have
that much time?
The screening’s
just four days away.
Wing: Gon, if I were a judge,
I would be very disappointed
if someone showed me
an improvised special attack.
( Gon gasps )
Wing: Now listen carefully.
No matter what happens,
you must not try
to emulate kurapika.
If you think about it,
i’m sure you won’t need me
to tell you why.
Gon: No, sir.
Wing: So just be yourself.
You’re powerful enough
on your own merits
that you really have no need
to imitate others.
Gon: You think so?
Wing: I do.
I want you to reflect
on each of the things
that you’re capable of.
If you do, you’ll find
the answer you’re looking for.
( Music slows, stops )
Uh...
Gon: I need a hint.
- Please? Just a little one?
- ( Wing chuckles )
You’re starting to sound
a little bit desperate.
( Gon sighs )
Wing: Haste makes waste,
but hard work always pays off.
Gon: Yeah, I agree with you.
But if it wasn’t
for this deadline...
Wing: All right,
then here’s a hint.
When you demonstrated your power
for this tsezguerra person,
it was just
your normal ren, right?
Gon: Yeah.
Wing: Next time, show him
everything at the same time.
Gon: Everything, sir?
Wing: Yes. Pay attention, gon.
Show him everything
you’ve learned...
At the same time.
♪
Gon: Everything i’ve learned
at the same time.
Ten, contain the aura
leaking out of the body.
Zetsu,
shut off the aura
by closing the nodes.
Ren,
bring forth
an incredible amount of aura.
And hatsu...
Wait.
Ren is bringing forth my aura,
but zetsu is suppressing it.
- If I do both at once...
- ( Music slows, stops )
- ( Thump )
- ( Killua gasps )
Did his brain short out again?
Get it together, gon.
If you take too long,
i’ll leave you behind.
Gon: How am I supposed
to summon something
and suppress it
at the same time?
( Groans )
Wing: I want you to reflect
on each of the things
that you’re capable of.
Gon: Hmm.
After Mr. Wing
helped unleash my nen,
I got seriously hurt in battle,
because all I really knew
how to do was ten...
But I mastered zetsu
in the process.
Then I learned gyo
so I could see through
hisoka’s special ability.
Gyo!
Oh, yeah!
I still have gyo!
Gyo, focused aura in your eyes
so you can see hidden aura.
( Gasps ) Focus?
That’s right.
I was so focused on my eyes
that I never thought
about trying to put aura
anywhere else.
There’s a little aura
being released.
If I can suppress the rest,
I can do them all at once.
Hmm.
♪
I did it!
( Gasps )
( Sighs )
It’s no use.
The second I relax,
it falls apart.
But it’s possible.
If I can just focus all the aura
built up through ren,
how much power could I have?
I want to see.
I have to try it out!
Wing: Haste makes waste, gon.
Gon: Mm.
Osu!
Killua: Sounds like
a breakthrough.
But you’re still
not gonna beat me.
Narrator: The two boys
are about to undergo
a brand-new awakening.
♪
( Singing in Japanese )