♪
Narrator: After he
parts ways with killua
in order to stop
the sorting process,
gon finds himself under attack
by new chimera ants.
Gon: An owl and a bat?
they’re both
nocturnal creatures,
hunters of the night.
From the left?
Bring it.
( Groans )
The owl’s feathers?
The bat’s wings are so loud,
I couldn’t hear the owl coming.
♪
( Singing in Japanese )
( Flapping )
( Owl ant laughs )
My ears can pick up sounds
of a higher frequency
than other animals’.
i hear you
stepping on dry leaves
and your clothes rustling.
they tell me
exactly where you are.
( Wings flapping )
Gon: From the right this time.
( Groans )
The owl distracts me
with its feathers
right before the bat strikes.
They’ve covered long-range
and close-up attacks.
Wait. That means...
( Both gasp )
Bat ant: All that aura
still won’t help you.
We rule the darkness.
Gon: I need a new approach.
If the owl is acting as backup,
i’ve gotta focus on the sound
of the bat’s wings.
Right after the owl attacks,
the bat strikes.
- ( Wings flap )
- now.
Spot on!
i missed?
But my timing was perfect.
Is it echolocation?
Damn. I missed again?
Bat ant: He’s correctly guessing
the direction of my attacks.
Sharp ears for a human.
Owl ant: And his aura
just keeps growing,
so my feathers
aren’t doing any damage.
Gon: It seems the bat
uses echolocation
to anticipate the timing
and angle of my attack.
If I don’t stop it,
I won’t be able to win.
( Inhales )
- Owl ant: Eh?
- Bat ant: Huh?
Gon: Okay, now, show me rock!
owl ant:
His aura is still growing.
This could pose a problem.
Bat ant: No, this is our chance.
That’s probably
his ultimate attack.
If we can evade it, we’ve won.
my echolocation
should be of great help.
Owl ant: Can I assist?
Bat ant: Hold on.
I’ll try getting closer
as quietly as I can.
Gon: The sound’s moving away.
It’s all gone.
Bat ant: Now without flapping,
a dive bomb.
Gon: No way.
Your wings are nothing
like the owl’s,
so I can hear you slicing
through the air as you fall.
bat ant: Well? Go on.
Show me your ultimate attack.
No reaction? ( Laughs )
Pathetic human ears.
In that case, I suppose
i’ll just slash your jugular.
Gon: Keep movement
to a minimum.
( Bat ant gasps )
Gon: Draw them
as close as possible.
Bat ant: He knew? This is bad.
At least his punch will take
a few milliseconds to land.
I have plenty of time
to fly away.
( Gon inhales )
( Screams )
( Bat ant gasps )
That noise!
I can’t see.
I have to escape.
Gon: Not so fast! Jan...
You aren’t the only one...
Ken...
Who can locate by sound.
Paper!
All right. Eh?
( Gasps )
A rock?
That’s how he
deflected my shot?
( Owl ant chuckles )
- That was a close one, huh?
- Gon: Damn.
Even my special attack
couldn’t bring it down.
( Owl ant grunting )
( Tone ringing )
( Gon groans )
What was that?
There was a sound
that made my head spin.
Is this ultrasound, too?
Bat ant: That stupid kid
is incredibly loud,
but when it comes to attacking
with sound, I can’t be beat.
Meleoron: This is why
they’re such a great team.
They strike with sound
and finish with brawn.
( Laughs )
Well, kid?
Gon: Do I plug my ears? No.
If I limit my hearing,
my reaction time will suffer.
I know. Gyo.
Owl ant: Eh? Glowing eyes?
No, it’s aura.
He’s focusing on sight
instead of hearing.
Bat ant: Let’s give him another.
Nauseating noise!
( Gon groans )
( Licks )
Okay. This should help
a little with the sound.
Bat ant: He spit on bits
of cloth to make earplugs.
Clever.
Water significantly weakens
the energy of sound.
( Gon groans )
All right. This is better.
I can locate the owl
through its aura.
There!
A feather?
( Gasps )
Zetsu. Of course.
They used to be wild animals.
they know
how to conceal themselves...
When stalking their prey.
I can fend off their attacks,
but the ultrasound really hurts.
If I don’t keep up the gyo,
they’ll take me down
before I can even find them.
meleoron:
In terms of latent aura,
this kid has a clear advantage.
Even after all those hits,
he’s still unharmed.
But his capability
is irrelevant.
Without a strategy,
he’s just a moving target.
Gon: They work in perfect sync.
I have to break it apart.
Owl ant: The fool must think
that staying really close to me
all the time
will prevent the Sonic attacks.
Bat ant: No such luck.
( Gon groaning )
gon: If I use rock,
I know can defeat this one,
but if I do, the bat might
run off and warn the other ants.
( Owl ant laughs )
To me, a starry night
is as bright as day.
as long as i’m
not in pitch darkness,
i can see you without
needing to rely on my hearing.
that means
that if I cover my ears...
Bat ant: I can attack at will!
meleoron: So the kid has
shrouded his entire body in aura
to avoid major damage,
but that greatly reduces
the strength of his attacks,
making it impossible
to stand against them.
He’s bound to lose
at this rate.
Maybe he’s a bad bet after all.
Gon: So their movements
are always in sync,
but that’s gonna be
their greatest weakness, too!
♪
Here.
They always take positions
on opposite sides
to avoid both
being targeted at once.
when the owl
is in front of me...
( Groans )
The bat is behind me!
( Bat ant groans )
A giant wall?
( Yelps )
Then the real wall...
Was behind me.
♪
Owl ant: He turned
our teamwork against us?
( Gasps )
Gon: With one opponent,
I can concentrate on attacking.
meleoron: Not bad
once he finds his rhythm,
but that attack won’t be enough
to get him anywhere, not here.
Owl ant: Damn.
( Panting )
Gon: Show me rock!
- jan, Ken...
- Owl ant: Why, you--
( gasps )
Rock!
( Meleoron gasps )
Gon: I made sure
to knock you west.
Go back to the ngl!
Meleoron: That was incredible.
I see.
So that’s his signature move.
I take it back.
He can be useful.
But how do I proceed?
♪
Killua: Diego’s been dethroned,
and now soldiers,
all of ’em brainwashed,
are slaughtering
whole villages!
Man: Diego has fallen?
Man #2: Seriously?
Man #3: Can’t be.
We all saw the soldiers
try to kill everyone.
Killua: There’s no time
to think about it.
Get outta here. Run!
Warn the people in other areas.
Go! Hurry!
Neferpitou: Who’s interfering?
meow, it was
from the southeast this time.
Some of my puppets
have been stopped.
He’s fast.
Well, whoever they are,
they’re unpredictable.
An assassin?
but it seems like
they’re acting on their own.
A decoy?
( Groans )
This is so annoying.
I wanna kill them!
♪
Shaiapouf: It’s a diversion,
so we shouldn’t go.
That much is clear.
Neferpitou: Think so?
Okay, but he isn’t
trying to lure us in.
Well, that’s not
my impression.
It’s like he’s
doing the utmost care
not to get caught.
Shaiapouf: It may all be
an act to draw you out,
or perhaps i’m overanalyzing,
but still...
( Sighs )
My anguish is intoxicating
as I wallow in my dilemma.
Such is the pitfall of logic,
nothing more.
Neferpitou: Eh?
shaiapouf:
The answer is quite simple.
Our duty is to protect the king.
We must focus on that and let
the other ants handle the rest.
( Door opens )
Leol: Is it our turn?
When we were injured and
on the run from the hunters,
you took us in, and you
even gave us instructions
on how to use
our newfound power.
It seems the time has come
to return the favor.
Neferpitou: Someone is out there
running around
and disabling my puppets.
Can you go and kill them?
Leol: You can count on me.
Neferpitou: Perfect. Take this.
We can’t use telepathy,
you see.
That’s how i’ll give you
updates on their location.
Leol: Right.
( Door opens )
( Door closes )
Menthuthuyoupi: Are you certain
that we can really trust them?
neferpitou: Mm-mmm.
Nope, not even a little bit.
But since they’re the ones
trying to earn our trust,
we can be sure
that they’ll be working hard
to carry out their mission.
Shaiapouf: However, they may
be waiting to betray us.
( Chuckles )
And in that case,
we should treat them
accordingly, shouldn’t we?
( Killua panting )
The closest village to here
is at two o’clock,
and the next ones
are at eight and ten.
Should I just skip them
and head for taba,
40 kilometers away?
be cautious,
and don’t get caught.
♪
I shouldn’t go this way.
( Knuckle groans )
This is bad.
i should have
taken care of him myself.
Shoot: What’s wrong?
Knuckle: Even now,
cheetu is racing
towards east gorteau
at top speed.
Must have slipped past
the hunters that replaced us.
Shoot: Is he headed towards us?
Knuckle: He’s not.
His current course
will take him far to the south
if he keeps it.
Shoot: Where are you going?
Knuckle: Don’t try to stop me,
’cause i’m
in a bad enough mood already.
As of yesterday,
the hunter association
has captured 319 chimera ants
operating outside the ngl.
Not bad, but Colt has confirmed
that unfortunately none of them
were squadron leaders.
according to him,
there are eight of them left
that would be
considered aggressive.
They’ve encountered four so far,
but every last one of them
was able to avoid
being killed or captured.
Cheetu is going to east gorteau
for a reason.
i’m willing to bet
that he knows the king is there.
I’m positive he’s choosing
to return to the service
of the king
in order to increase
his own power.
My ability is still in effect
for the time being,
and i’m a lot stronger
than he is,
but if we let him
slip away from us
and he can gain even more power
before we meet again,
then all bets are off.
Plus if we allow
any more ants like him
to join up
with the king’s forces,
then we’ll never be able
to draw the royal guard away.
Still wanna stop me?
Do your best,
but i’m not gonna
make it easy for you. Uh...
shoot: First we
should contact Mr. Morel.
If worse comes to worst,
he’ll need to have adequate time
to find replacements for us.
I’m coming with you.
This should increase the odds
of us capturing that ant.
( Knuckle chuckles )
It’s knuckle.
Something’s come up.
Yes, I guess so. Probably.
Yeah, so, uh...
- ( Hangs up )
- Hello? Hello?
( Groans )
Morel: Fools!
I thought I told you
to send likke.
there’s no one
more suited for this than him.
Huh? Yeah, well,
I don’t give a damn.
Knov: Something wrong?
Morel: The chimera ant that we
were tracking has escaped.
Guess the review board
didn’t send over the hunter
that we requested.
Knov: And who did
they send instead?
Morel: Some hunter
i’ve never heard of,
probably just a temp.
Knov: A temp?
You mean hired hunters
who only take assigned jobs
through the hunter association?
Not surprisingly,
they have less talent.
Morel: Damn it.
i should have just
gone to talk to likke myself.
Knov: Come on now.
Stop being so foolish.
Bear in mind that if we
go over the board’s head,
the chairman is the one
who’s going to get saddled
with all of the blame.
He had to argue with the board
just to get us here.
i can’t imagine
it would go well for him.
Morel: Yeah, but they don’t
understand the situation here.
it’s based on donations
and who did what way back when.
knov: Yes,
but that’s no surprise.
the board
has always been inflexible.
morel: How the hell
can you be so relaxed, huh?
If we underestimate
the squadron leaders,
we’ll pay dearly for it.
fact of the matter
is these things are tough,
and they know what they want.
And that’s not all.
They have the talent
to quickly master the abilities
they need the most.
it’ll be too late
if we leave it up to the board.
They’re too mindful
of their own interests.
Well, maybe failure is
exactly what they want here.
Knov: Are you referring
to the rumors going around
that the vice-chairman’s
faction is bribing the board?
and furthermore that
they’re only handing out work
to those hunters
who have agreed to vote for him
in the next election,
no matter what? Is that right?
There’s no evidence
of that happening.
Morel: Ha ha! You think they’re
stupid enough to get caught?
Look at the facts.
The squadron leaders,
every single one of them
they’ve faced has escaped alive.
if we don’t succeed,
the chairman will be blamed.
He’ll take the fall
for everything.
The vice-chairman’s supporters
will do anything
to guarantee that.
The more victims
the ants claim,
the louder the voices
screaming for his resignation.
Meanwhile, they’re just kicking
back in their office chairs.
Knov: Hmm.
morel:
If we can take out the king,
but five million people
are already dead,
then we’ve totally failed!
Knov: Yes. We already knew that.
The chairman is prepared.
When he devised this plan,
he was fully aware
of the consequences.
He knew exactly how much time
assuring victory would take
and how many casualties.
( Morel groans )
Five million’s on the low end.
That’s still too high.
( Cellphone rings )
Mr. Marcos?
What?
Marcos: The damn phones
have been ringing nonstop.
And that’s not all.
Rumors of a coup d’etat
are flying around!
It’s been discovered
that mass murders
are taking place
all over the country.
It’s no rumor. I mean,
it’s actually happening.
What is going on here?
Tell me, are you responsible?
Morel: We haven’t done anything.
Did the public find out
about the sorting?
- ( Alarm blaring )
- We’ll talk later on.
now go back
to your office immediately.
- Knov: Morel.
- Morel: Huh?
Announcer: Good evening.
The dearly beloved leader
of our land, Diego,
has an urgent announcement
to make.
to ensure
that our great leader’s message
will be heard clearly
throughout the nation,
we request that all
relay speakers in all regions
be turned to maximum volume.
All televisions and radios
should be on
and the volume raised
to its maximum setting.
Diego: Good evening,
my beloved citizens.
I’m Diego.
I have declared east gorteau
is now officially
under martial law.
this precaution
is to combat malcontents
that would foment rebellion.
i ask you not to leave
your residence for any reason.
Lock your doors.
Anyone outdoors
without permission
will be labeled a rebel
and severely punished.
I implore you, turn a deaf ear
to the false rumors
being circulated,
and follow my instructions.
the soldiers
of my special forces
will soon be visiting
your residences
to see if any rebels
are hiding inside.
No one else should be allowed
inside of your residences.
Knov: That happened too quickly.
Morel: Looks like gon and killua
took matters
into their own hands.
Knov: This must be part
of the chimera ants’ plan.
They were so well-prepared,
it makes sense.
Their plans took into account
people finding out about it.
it would give them
all the excuse they needed
to use overt military control.
And now east gorteau
has officially been placed
under martial law,
completely isolating them
from the rest of the world,
cutting them off entirely.
♪
Killua: Hah!
Yeah, bring it on,
tanks, jets, whatever
the hell else you’ve got.
I’ll take all of ’em down.
( Singing in Japanese )