Queen: Your first mission
will be to lead all the soldiers
here to capture my food.
I want you to capture
more of those highly
nutritious organisms for me.
Squadron leader: I shall.
♪
( Singing in Japanese )
Narrator: The chimera ants are
insatiable carnivores which are
currently under the designated
quarantine level one.
Once these creatures
have evolved
beyond two meters in length,
humans no longer
stand a chance.
( Farmer sighs )
Huh?
Huh.
( Insects buzzing )
Hey, what the hell is that?
Farmer #2: Huh?
( Farmers yelling )
Squadron leader:
Target the fully grown ones!
They will provide
the most nutrition. Now go!
♪
( Farmer #1 yells )
( Farmer #3 grunts )
( All yelling )
Man: Look out! Look out!
( Men screaming )
Kite: A chimera ant queen
stays on the move
until she finds
a site she likes.
During her search,
she’ll produce
more and more soldier ants,
building her own personal army.
Once she’s chosen a location,
she produces a swarm
of construction ants
to build her castle
with incredible speed.
She will then remain within
that fortress until her death.
Should a queen who has
reached two meters in height
develop a taste for human flesh,
no one is safe.
Entire towns and villages
will go missing,
victims of the queen’s
limitless hunger.
Spin: Nothing so far.
I just finished checking out
the past six months,
and the largest group
I could find only numbered ten.
Gon: Hey, can we try looking
for missing people individually?
Spin: Don’t be ridiculous.
You know how many
hundreds of thousands of people
go missing worldwide each year?
Killua: We could
still see which areas
have the highest
concentrations, though.
Spin: Mm, well...
No good.
This data is two years old.
Gon: Maybe we should start
by checking for sightings.
Killua: Yeah,
seeing a two-meter-tall insect
would be a big deal.
Spin: Sure,
that goes without saying,
but we tried that already.
We didn’t turn up anything.
Banana: We might be getting all
worked up over nothing, guys.
Spin: Maybe so.
Kite: Bring up
all the tidal data
from the day the arm was found.
Spin: It was discovered
right around here.
Kite: Now try going back
to ten days ago.
Locate any currents that could
potentially have carried the arm
to that location
in that period of time.
Spin: Wait. What do you mean?
Kite: I mean
that we should consider
the possibility
the arm was severed
after the chimera ant
washed up somewhere else.
Spin: I see.
Seems it could have come
from any of the balsa islands.
Kite: And unfortunately
that includes the mitene union.
Stick: Seriously?
Banana: Oh! Where the n.G.L.
Autonomous region is.
Kite: Yes, and that’s
not to mention east gorteau.
No chance of getting information
out of those two countries.
Killua: What’s the n.G.L.?
Banana: N.G.L.’s an acronym
that stands for Neo-green life.
Stick: It’s a country
founded by people
who reject modern technology,
choosing instead
to live in nature.
Spin: Here it is.
♪
They primarily
communicate by mail,
and primary travel
is by horseback.
Anyone who brings technology
into the country
could be executed.
Like back in ’87, there was
a three-man television crew
that was caught trying
to enter the country
in order to get a story.
One was executed,
and two are still jailed.
99% of its
2.17 million population
belong to the n.G.L. Party.
The rest are volunteers.
Kite: Let’s assume for now
that the chimera ant
washed ashore there.
How would
the n.G.L.’s citizenry react?
I doubt they’d do anything.
When a deadly epidemic
spread through the area,
they refused
international medical aid,
because they preferred
to let nature
run its grisly course instead.
Even if they tried to contact
the outside world,
it would be too late
by the time word arrived.
So if the arm
that was discovered did belong
to the chimera ant queen,
then it’s entirely possible
that she’s already begun
constructing her nest.
Squadron leader: A contest?
Alligator ant:
Yeah, between you and me.
Just a friendly challenge
to see which one of us
can bring the queen
more humans to devour.
- What do you say, huh?
- ( Squadron leader scoffs )
Alligator ant: Hmm?
You’re running away?
Accept my challenge!
Squadron leader: What?
Are you ordering me around?
Tell me. Why should I follow
an order from you?
I only follow orders given to me
by the queen herself.
Alligator ant:
Oh, give me a break.
You’re just scared of losing.
See, my squad is comprised
of elite soldiers.
I can beat any squad
in this entire castle.
Hey, I know!
I should get the other
squad leaders in on this,
make it a group thing.
If we all compete
against each other,
we’re bound
to capture more prey.
Squadron leader:
So that’s the goal?
I see.
I agree with your premise.
If we gather more prey,
the queen will be
quite pleased indeed.
Alligator ant: Well, okay, then.
That settles it.
Squadron leader: However,
the quality of the prey
matters as well.
It’s very important
to ensure that the queen eats
only highly nutritious humans.
Alligator ant: That guy’s such
a stiff, it’s not even funny.
Turtle ant: But that’s
what makes him so endearing.
He’s as loyal
as he is dedicated to the cause.
Bird ant: I presume
that the human
from which he was created
was also quite earnest.
( Mother crying )
Farmer: Oh.
Where are you going?!
I told you to get
some rest, didn’t I?!
Farmer #2:
I’ll go bring her back.
Elder: Don’t bother.
It won’t help.
Farmer #2: But she’s been going
to the forest
every single morning
and spending
her whole day searching.
Farmer #1: That’s right.
She’ll probably collapse
from exhaustion soon.
Elder: But she still can’t stop
looking for
her missing children.
That’s what it means
to be a parent.
Farmer #2:
How long has it been now?
How many days ago
did Kurt and reina vanish?
Farmer #1: It’s like the spirits
whisked them away.
- ( Children laughing )
- Boy: Yeah!
Girl: Huh?
Wow. Those bugs are big.
Boy: Huh?
Squadron leader: It’s an area
we haven’t raided yet.
♪
( Girl screams )
( Mother grunts )
( Squadron leader gasps )
( Mother sobs )
( Man screams )
Girl: Mommy!
Farmer #1: It was them,
those awful monsters!
They must have been the ones
that stole your children
from you!
( Mother gasps )
( Elder grunts )
( Crowd murmuring )
Turtle ant: Excellent.
The queen will be most pleased.
This will be
more than sufficient, i’m sure.
- ( Gunfire )
- ( Gasps )
( Hostages screaming )
( Turtle ant gasps ) What?
Gunman: Exterminate
the insects quickly.
Gunman #2:
That’s gyro’s direct order.
Turtle ant: Gyro?
What is gyro?!
Gunman #3: The name of our king,
you fool!
Damn it.
♪
Spin: Okay, I just bought us
tickets to the mitene union.
Banana: But in order
for us to reach the n.G.L.,
it looks like we’ll
have to take an airship
to the neighboring
rokario Republic,
and then we can travel by land
the rest of the way.
Stick: Well, those nasty rumors
"ant" gonna help.
Just kidding. ( Laughs )
Killua: Nasty rumors?
Gon: Like what?
Kite: Have you heard of d.D.?
Gon: Uh, no.
Kite: It’s a drug
propagating rapidly
in urban areas worldwide.
It’s derived from the bira tree,
which is native
to the mitene union.
And not only are they
native to the region,
but they claim over 80%
of the world’s bira trees
are located in the n.G.L.
Killua: Okay,
so the nasty rumors
are that the n.G.L.
Is manufacturing it?
Kite: They’re still only rumors.
No one has been able
to prove it publicly yet.
Stick: The country
is locked down tight.
Spin: When anybody tries
to get in and investigate,
they’re instantly executed.
Gon: They are?
Pokkle: He wasn’t killed?
- Ponzu: Hmm?
- Man: No.
If he had been captured
trying to uncover
the n.G.L.’s secrets,
then there’s a good chance
he would have been executed
like that TV crew man.
Man #2: But this reporter
wore a recording device.
Our goal was to intercept
the final message,
and that’s how we did it.
When the message was played...
Reporter: M-monsters!
Gigantic bugs!
( Static crackling )
Pokkle: Gigantic bugs, huh?
Man #1: Mm.
So what do you think?
Pokkle: Hmm. I can’t be sure
without knowing a lot more.
- ( Chuckles )
- Men: Huh?
Pokkle: I’ll have
to see for myself.
I mean, I am the only
magical-beast hunter here.
Man #1: That settles it.
I’ll go get three tickets
for the journey.
- Ponzu: Make it four.
- Men: Huh?
Pokkle: Ponzu?
Ponzu: I’m coming with you guys.
Pokkle: You can’t!
This is too dangerous!
You don’t even have
a professional license yet,
and we’re talking about
the n.G.L. Here, remember?
Ponzu: And that’s why.
You’re not allowed
to bring technology
into the n.G.L., right,
so if they catch you
with any cell phones
or wireless communicators,
guaranteed you’ll be
arrested on the spot.
All i’m saying
is if there’s any trouble,
you guys’ll need me,
or rather, you’ll need them.
( Buzzing )
If you have
a letter for someone,
they can carry it
anywhere you like.
( Pokkle chuckles )
I get it.
They’ll sure come in handy.
( Indistinct announcements )
Kite: It may be
too late to ask this,
but are you sure
you want to come along?
Gon: Of course!
Killua: You weren’t kidding
about the "late" part, huh?
Kite: As you know,
we have no idea
what the situation is
inside the n.G.L.
There may very well be
a swarm of giant chimera ants
already hunting humans down,
and if that does indeed
turn out to be the case,
then my priority
will be saving them,
so be aware that I may
not be able to help you two.
If you’re going to join us,
you must be able
to protect yourselves.
Gon: Right. I got it.
Killua: We’re okay.
Kite: And if it happens to be me
who finds himself in danger,
then leave me there.
Gon: Uh...
Kite: You got it?
♪
( Squadron leader gasps )
Alligator ant: Hey,
that’s a pretty good haul.
Well, it’s less than half
of what my squadron delivered,
but it’s okay.
Squadron leader:
My focus was quality,
and I wasn’t competing with you.
( Alligator ant scoffs )
Whatever.
So anyway, did you hear?
That turtle guy’s group ran into
a bit of human resistance.
Squadron leader: You don’t say.
( Page turns )
Bird ant: Hmm. What you saw
were probably things
called guns.
Turtle ant: Guns?
Bird ant: To put it simply,
it’s a barrel
that launches small
metal projectiles, or bullets,
using the explosive force
of gunpowder.
It’s one of the most commonly
used human weapons.
Turtle ant: I have no idea
what you’re talking about.
Bird ant: If you want to know
more, then read these books.
They’re wonderful and filled
with quite useful information,
such as how humans
think, behave,
and function as a society.
Turtle ant: Maybe you can answer
a question for me, then.
These humans,
do they have armies, too?
Bird ant: Why do you ask?
Turtle ant: Well, because what
attacked us out there
was an army. That much I know.
They belong to a military body
led by an authoritative figure,
much like us.
Oh, yes,
and I have another question.
They mentioned
something about a name?
Bird ant: A name? Hmm.
I can see why you’re confused.
It’s a human idea and one that
we do not make use of ourselves.
In terms you would understand...
Alligator ant:
It seems humans are capable
of more than we thought.
I was beginning to think
all they could do
was cry and run away.
Squadron leader:
And why does that surprise you?
You and I are quite different
ourselves, are we not?
It’s only natural
that humans would have
unique traits as well.
Their blood, after all,
flows through all of our veins.
( Tone ringing )
Queen: Squadron leaders,
assemble!
Squadron leaders, assemble!
Bird ant: The queen
is summoning us.
Queen: Squadron leaders,
assemble!
Cat ant: Do you get a headache
every time the queen calls
to us, or am I the only one?
Lobster ant: No, my ears
start ringing like crazy
whenever I hear it.
Scorpion ant: A shame, really.
If only the queen
could talk like we do.
♪
Queen: I shall now
begin preparation
for the birth of the king.
Every day from this day forward,
you will deliver me 50 humans.
Chimera ants: Yes, majesty!
Turtle ant: Your majesty,
may I ask a question?
Queen: Yes. Speak.
Turtle ant: Among the humans
are soldiers like ourselves,
my queen,
with weapons to use against us.
If I may make a suggestion,
we must fortify our defenses
in preparation
for a potential attack.
We have already come up
with a few options.
Would you care to hear them?
Queen: I will allow you
to decide your own course.
For now, I must focus
entirely on my son.
( Turtle ant gasps )
Thank you, your majesty.
But one more thing,
may we have your permission
to have names?
Queen: And what is a name?
Turtle ant:
It’s like a label, my queen,
one that can be used to identify
each of us individually.
Queen: Fine. Do as you please.
Turtle ant:
I am eternally grateful.
Queen: Curious creatures.
They’re assertive
and desire things called names
to be distinct.
They place a high value
on individualism,
yet strive with one another
for the good of the colony.
I suppose i’m just as peculiar
to find this change fascinating.
Perhaps, just perhaps,
I, too, have faint traces
of human blood within me.
Regardless, I cannot help
but feel great anticipation.
Yes. I can sense you already,
almost as if recalling
a memory from my own past.
I promise you this,
you shall stand at the pinnacle
of all species!
Names, amusing little things.
The three elite royal guards,
I shall come up
with a name for you myself.
( Airship whirring )
Killua: Well,
what did you just decide?
Gon: You remember
what kite said before we left,
that we should escape
without him if he’s in danger?
Killua: Yeah. He didn’t make it
sound like it was a choice.
Gon: Right,
and that’s why neither one of us
felt comfortable
saying anything.
But there’s something
that i’ve been thinking about.
Do you really think kite,
a guy ging respects,
can ever actually be
in that much danger?
You said before
that ging had a reason
for bringing
kite and me together.
So do you still think that?
Killua: Yeah.
Gon: Lately i’ve started
to think you’re right.
I don’t know the reason,
and maybe I never will,
but I can’t give up.
And it doesn’t matter
what’s going on here.
I just don’t want
to disappoint ging, you know?
Or me. I couldn’t
forgive myself, either.
I won’t run away.
That’s what i’ve decided.
( Killua gasps )
Damn it.
You had such
a serious look on your face,
I was expecting something big,
but it’s
the same stuff as usual.
Gon: Huh?
I thought about it a lot.
I even ran a bunch
of simulations in my head.
Killua: Think all you want,
you’re still gon.
If someone said
you should abandon them,
there’s no way you’d ever do it.
( Gon sighs )
You make it sound like I
wasted my time considering it.
Okay, then, so what about you?
Killua: Don’t know.
I guess i’d just think about it
when the time comes.
Gon: Hold on.
You mean you might run away?
Killua: Depends on what happens.
Look, I don’t really do
these hypotheticals.
Gon: Fine, but what if--
killua: Look,
I already told you.
I don’t know what i’d do, okay?
I never decide ’til it’s time.
♪
Narrator: And so, the airship,
along with the group and
all of its other passengers,
begins the journey
for the mitene union
still completely unaware
of the cruel fate
which lies in store for them.
♪
( Singing in Japanese )