Ging: All i’m doing
is following
the old man’s wishes,
and i’m not looking
for any trouble.
Beans: Mr. Ging,
why would you do all of this
if not to change the result?
Ging: When I can make
my quarry move how I want,
i’ve succeeded as a hunter.
♪
( Singing in Japanese )
♪ You can smile again
( singing in Japanese )
♪ You can fly away
♪
Narrator: On August eighth,
at precisely 12 A.M.
The voting
to elect a 13th chairman
who would succeed netero
began inside the hunter
association headquarters.
The rules were set by ging,
and one provision
made all 661 members
both voter and candidate.
On this day, voter turnout
was below the required 95%,
and the rules stated
that a revote must be held.
However, the second vote
also failed
to meet the requirements,
and of course, as per the rules,
the process
would have to start again.
Pariston: Looking at the results
from the first
two rounds of voting,
I have two proposals.
One, have Mr. Beans
review all ballots
in order to reduce
the number of invalid votes.
Two, hunters who break the rules
by abstaining
or submitting invalid votes
will have their licenses
temporarily confiscated.
Now, what do all of you
think about that?
Saiyu: If we
implement the first,
do we still need the second?
I mean, just getting rid
of the invalid votes
would put us over 95%.
Pariston: Eh, i’m not so sure.
Some hunters may play hooky
when they learn they
can’t submit invalid votes.
There are people who want
to spit on netero’s wishes.
Kanzai: Wait. What?
Mizaistom: Drop it.
You’re just gonna drag this out.
Pariston: I’m sorry.
Did I say something wrong?
The former chairman declared
that a 95% turnout was required.
Invalid votes and no-shows
disrespect his memory.
Kanzai: No! They just don’t want
to see you become the chairman!
Don’t you get it?
Pariston:
Then they should exercise
their right to vote
for someone else.
I’m certain that there are other
qualified candidates out there,
though it appears
that the majority
of hunters may disagree.
It’s possible,
with your limited vocabulary
and math skills,
that’s hard to grasp.
( Kanzai growls )
( Geru hisses )
Mizaistom: I said
don’t drag this out.
This is your warning, kanzai.
Cheadle:
I think we should take the time
to broadcast
each candidate’s message
before we start
adding new rules.
Abstaining and
casting invalid votes
aren’t really violations.
Pariston: I fully agree
with your first statement,
but the second makes me wonder
if I heard you right.
I can’t imagine that you,
miss cheadle,
the faction leader
for the former chairman,
would speak that way.
The former chairman said
the election’s
difficulty level would be d,
which means that,
for us starred hunters,
this should be
a relatively simple task.
Relax. The chairman
trusted us to handle this,
and i’m confident we will.
Cluck: Pariston, you’re a pain!
Don’t talk! Shut up!
Piyon: It shows
that he trusts the zodiacs,
so we really
shouldn’t read any more
into the difficulty level
than that.
"S" means get moving.
An "f" means
he’s really challenging us.
Saiyu: Look,
spin it however you want,
but nobody’s actually violated
the rules here, scumbag.
Pariston: I call them violations
as a wake-up call
to all those
who might think that they’re
respecting the former chairman
by trying to gum up the works.
I want them to know
they owe it to him
to make this election
run smoothly and quickly.
Kanzai: Then say it
during your speech.
It’s coercion to make it
part of the damn rules!
Pariston: Is coercion
such a bad thing
when you think about it?
Mizaistom: Right.
Got it. We’re done.
I would be quite content
with either suggestion.
I know our motivations
are very different,
but I do agree that
all hunters should participate,
unless they have
a good reason not to.
Pariston: Okay.
I say we vote on it.
- Cheadle: One thing.
- Pariston: Hmm?
Cheadle: What’s to stop you
from claiming
that those who have
had their licenses confiscated
shouldn’t be
counted as hunters?
You wouldn’t try anything
that silly, would you?
♪
Pariston: Of course not!
I would never dream of using
such underhanded tactics
to manipulate the vote.
We’ll just hold licenses.
That’s all.
- Mizaistom: And lost licenses?
- Pariston: Hmm?
Mizaistom:
A pro hunter knows better
than to lose their license.
If they do,
they may be a screw-up,
but they still remain a hunter
under the official bylaws.
Pariston: Hmm. Now let’s see.
It sounds like you’re saying
that someone could use
the threat of a hunter license
going missing
to manipulate the election.
Sadly, that’s just
not something we can prevent.
Make a note of this
in the minutes, please!
Even those hunters who have
misplaced their licenses
will still be able
to cast their vote!
That way, we guarantee
that no one can manipulate
the turnout or the majority.
Problem solved.
( Cheadle sighs )
I hate to admit it,
but unless we do something
to get out the vote,
we’ll never be able to wipe that
smirk off of pariston’s face.
Ginta, cluck, and piyon
are manipulating
the votes for themselves.
That much is obvious.
But if they can’t pull it off,
we’re all screwed.
I am furious with myself
for thinking this,
but part of me
wishes that ging were here.
He’s a monster,
and he’s out of control.
Why did the chairman select him,
of all people,
to be the vice-chairman?
Netero: Since I can pick
my second-in-command myself,
it would be
boring to have a yes man.
It should be someone
I can’t even stand to look at.
That’s exactly
the kind of person
I want to have at my side.
Beans: Chairman, i’m sorry,
but, even now, I still
believe it was a big mistake.
Seaquant:
Young master killua’s back?
That’s a relief.
When I saw his name
on the list of absentee hunters,
I got worried.
How’s he doing?
Hmm?
♪
( Rumbling )
He opened the testing gates
up to the fifth door?
Zebro: Actually, his expression
was what concerned me.
He looked incredibly distressed.
I couldn’t even summon
the courage to speak to him.
If you run into
his friend there,
could you relay
a message for me?
I want you to ask him if he
can help young master killua.
Seaquant: Well...
Hate to tell you, but his
friend’s why he’s so upset.
( Zebro gasps )
Gon is? That’s impossible.
Young master.
( Wind blowing )
Killua: Let me see alluka.
I need her help.
Silva: Killua.
Killua: I don’t have time
for this, dad.
I’m going either way.
Come with me.
Silva: Forget it.
No one alive
can control alluka.
Killua: And i’m telling you
you’re wrong!
You and big brother.
Alluka’s a member of the family,
not a machine!
I’m going.
I’ll ask her as her brother.
Silva: You’ll "ask"? Really?
That entity isn’t human.
Don’t ever
think of it as family.
Killua: Wh-what did you say?
( Beast roars )
♪
Silva: That thing...
Is something
from another place...
Something from the darkness.
( Beast growling )
Killua: Oh, sit down.
Gon made an awful contract
putting conditions on his nen.
An exorcist would die
trying to fix it.
If alluka hasn’t changed,
i’m the only one
who can help her. I know it.
And gon needs her help
right now to live.
Silva: Promise me one thing,
that you will never betray
your friends.
Killua: If I can help out
a friend, but choose not to...
Is that a betrayal?
Silva: Come with me.
♪
( Footsteps echoing )
I’m sure you already know this,
but demands
are still being made.
Killua: And who made
the last wish?
Silva: Milluki.
He asked for the newest computer
available at the time.
I verified the wish was made
when I made a deal with him,
so it’s not a lie.
Killua: A computer, huh?
Well, that’s not so bad.
Was it because illumi was
manipulating me? Is that why?
What have I done?
How could I leave my little
sister in this situation?
Silva: Kil, I want
to confirm this once more.
What are the rules
to alluka’s wishes?
Killua: It’s fine.
I know alluka
better than anybody else.
Silva: It’s necessary. Have you
forgotten how many have died?
Killua: We’ve killed
more than that, and you know it!
Silva: Killua...
If you can’t keep yourself calm,
this ends right here.
Our word matters to me,
because I care for you.
As your father,
it’s only natural
that I should be concerned.
So please, confirm the rules.
Killua: Alluka.
( Birds chirping )
Alluka: Mitsuba. Mitsuba!
Pick me up!
Mitsuba: Yes, of course.
Are you ready?
Up you go!
Alluka: There! Go up there!
Mitsuba: Very well.
Alluka: Fly me high, okay?
Mitsuba: Yes. There you go!
Alluka: Mitsuba.
Mitsuba: I hear you,
young master alluka. What?
♪
Yes. Master alluka’s face
suddenly changed!
Killua: Oh. It’s fine.
I’ll handle it.
Alluka,
you think you could
fly me up really high?
Alluka: ’kay.
Up, up, and away.
Okay!
Killua: Back to normal.
Please keep this a secret.
Mitsuba: Oh, i’m afraid
I already told your mother.
Killua: Huh?!
But it was me
and alluka’s secret!
♪
Mrs. Zoldyck: Do what
she demands three times?
Killua: Mm-hmm.
And then her eyes
turn all black.
Silva: After alluka
lifts you up,
they go back to normal?
Killua: Nuh-uh. After that,
alluka grants you one wish.
It can be anything.
I didn’t get it at first,
but then I figured
I could just wish
for her to tell me how
to turn her eyes back to normal,
and so alluka told me.
Silva: Do you remember
exactly what she said?
It’s important.
Killua:
"If I Grant you one wish,
"then my eyes will turn white.
"As soon as you fulfill
three demands,
they will turn
completely black."
Mrs. Zoldyck: Refuse any demands
alluka makes for now,
no matter how small they are.
Mitsuba: Of course.
I understand, ma’am.
Alluka: Hey, mitsuba!
Pick me up!
Mitsuba: I’m sorry,
young master, but I can’t.
Alluka: Then...
Shake my hand, okay?
Mitsuba: Oh, uh...
I can’t do that either,
young master.
Forgive me.
Alluka: Then just give me
a piggyback ride, okay?
Mitsuba: I’m sorry. I can’t.
Oh, what should I do?
( Alluka sighs )
Mitsuba: It’s okay.
Why don’t we go catch
some bugs and play? All right?
Alluka: Then, mitsuba,
can you fly me real high?
Mitsuba: I’m afraid I can’t,
young ma--
( killua gasps )
( Butlers scream )
♪
Mrs. Zoldyck:
She was outside and...
Hassam
in the butlers’s quarters.
Silva: So two people
in different locations
who were both crushed instantly
at the same time.
Mrs. Zoldyck:
Silva, what’s happening?
Killua: It’s ’cause she said no.
She turned down alluka’s
demands, all four of ’em.
Alluka: Yasuha,
give me a piggyback ride!
Yasuha: Of course, young master.
( Gasps )
Young master alluka...
Can you please
make me a millionaire?
Could you maybe do that for me?
Alluka: ’kay.
♪
( Yasuha gasps )
( Gasping )
Alluka: ’kay?
Reporter: A blimp transporting
several million dollars
suddenly disappeared
this afternoon.
When it was recovered,
the money that had been inside
was mysteriously missing.
The pilot and crew members
have provided
baffling explanations
of the incident.
It may be some time before
the exact cause is determined.
Yasuha: I’m so very sorry!
I don’t know what came over me.
Illumi: A coincidence?
Well, that’s
a bit hard to believe.
Silva: When alluka is with us...
Mrs. Zoldyck: Not a single
demand is ever made of us.
Illumi: Dad, the next Butler,
do you think
I could pick them out?
So you’ve got one job,
to fulfill
all of alluka’s demands.
Butler: Yes. I understand.
Illumi: If you’re able
to clear this mission,
i’ll spare both you
and your lover as I promised.
Alluka: Hey, kasuga...
( Kasuga gasps )
Yes? What is it?
Alluka: Can you give me
your liver, please?
Kasuga: What?
Uh, that’s not--
I mean, it’s a bit--
alluka: No, huh?
Then, kasuga,
can you give me your intestines?
Please! Just wait a minute,
young master!
Here. Why don’t we play
another game, all right?
Alluka: Huh? Not that either?
( Kasuga shudders )
Alluka: Then, kasuga,
give me your spine!
( Kasuga gasping )
Young master!
I’m begging you!
Please, young master!
Alluka: Then, kasuga...
Give me your brain, please?
( Kasuga screams )
♪
Killua: Fulfill
three of alluka’s demands,
and she grants you one wish.
The wishes she can Grant
are probably limitless.
We’re pretty sure
that she can do anything.
But the bigger the wish
made to alluka is...
The bigger alluka’s
next demands will be.
In other words, an even trade.
And the price, the consequence
incurred by the wish...
Has to be paid back
by the next person.
♪
Refuse four
of her demands in a row,
that person dies, along with
the person they love the most.
In other words, at least
two people die simultaneously.
The bigger the wish,
the more people die
when the demands
aren’t fulfilled.
After that wish,
67 people died that we knew of.
( Alluka sighs )
♪
( Singing in Japanese )