( Whooshing )
Narrator:
The recently revived king,
now calling himself meruem,
headed back to the palace
to recover his memories
with pouf and youpi in tow.
♪
Palm: I can see
pouf’s main body.
It’s with the king.
( Knuckle gasps )
Palm: They’re heading
toward the palace
at an incredible speed.
( Knuckle growls )
That can only mean one thing.
The chairman lost.
If he couldn’t do it,
what can the rest of us do?
♪
( Singing in Japanese )
Komugi: I wish someone
would tell me what’s happening.
Where did the dear leader go?
Meruem: It won’t
stop following us.
The sight of it annoys me.
Menthuthuyoupi:
It’s the enemy’s power, sire.
I think the only way
that we can get it to disappear
is to hurt the enemy himself.
Meruem: Ah. Interesting.
Then let’s find out.
( Shaiapouf gasps )
Menthuthuyoupi: Incredible.
Is that really my--
( Gasps )
( Shaiapouf gasps )
Meruem: I see.
Menthuthuyoupi: I was wrong.
My power was never meant
for me to use.
It was meant to be used
by the king himself.
- Meruem: Youpi.
- Menthuthuyoupi: Huh?
Meruem: This doesn’t
make any sense.
- Menthuthuyoupi: Eh?
- ( Shaiapouf gasps )
Meruem: You were already
aware that this power
was the result
of an enemy attack,
and for you to know that,
you either saw it used,
or it was used
on you personally.
So which is it?
♪
Menthuthuyoupi: I saw him
and was hit by an attack.
( Shaiapouf gasps )
Meruem: It’s not on you now.
That thing is
not following you anymore,
so why does the enemy
still draw breath?
( Menthuthuyoupi stammers )
Meruem: I want you to tell me
how you deactivated
the enemy’s ability.
Well?
( Menthuthuyoupi sighs )
Okay, the truth is
we made an agreement.
In exchange for releasing me
from his power,
I agreed to spare his comrade.
Meruem: Then,
after he released you,
you had the opportunity
to finish his comrade
and him as well.
Why didn’t you do so?
Menthuthuyoupi:
Honestly, I have no idea.
I suppose I felt
like I couldn’t lose
to the enemy in any way.
I thought breaking a promise,
even a promise I made
to one of my enemies,
would be like
conceding defeat.
Shaiapouf: Ridiculous!
You deliberately passed up
the perfect opportunity
to remove every last threat
to the king,
all because
of some ambiguous feeling?
Menthuthuyoupi:
Punish me however you want.
I deserve it.
There is no excuse
for what I did.
Meruem: I only ordered
that you not lie to me.
You told the truth.
I won’t punish you
for your honesty.
You did just as I asked of you.
Menthuthuyoupi: Ah?
( Shaiapouf gasps )
Meruem: Now, pouf.
Shaiapouf: Sire.
- Meruem: Youpi.
- Menthuthuyoupi: Sire!
Meruem: Our relationships
have become quite complex.
( Both gasp )
Meruem: It seems
that our bodies and souls
have become intertwined,
and, as a result of this fact,
there can be no more secrets
between us.
Menthuthuyoupi: Sire!
Shaiapouf: Sire.
Meruem: Let’s go.
Both: Right.
Shaiapouf: Sire,
have you somehow realized
what it is I plan to do?
Was that meant as some sort
of final warning?
Do you sense how my guilt
tears away at me?
Nevertheless, even if it means
I am executed for my crime...
I do this for the king!
( Segments muttering )
- Find her.
- Find her quickly.
- Hurry up. Find her.
- Hurry up, and find her.
Shaiapouf: For the sake
of our species...
Segment: Find her.
- Find her quickly.
- Find her.
Shaiapouf: She is not necessary.
Segment: Where is she?
Shaiapouf:
I do this for the king.
- Segment: There? No.
- Is she over there?
( Chatter continues )
Knuckle: Hey there.
( Segments gasp )
Knuckle: I’ve got you pegged.
You can’t hurt me
when you’re split up, can you?
♪
( Stammers )
Where are you going?!
I’m talking to you!
You can’t remove a.P.R.
’til you beat me!
Shaiapouf: Youpi, the enemy
has just appeared before me.
He attached this thing,
but can he teleport, too?
Menthuthuyoupi:
No, that’s somebody else.
There’s one who can make himself
and everyone
around him invisible.
He looks just like a chameleon.
I don’t know his name,
but he’s a squadron leader,
which means he’s a traitor.
Shaiapouf: So you
spared a traitor?
Those humans, I might have been
able to forgive, but never this.
( Menthuthuyoupi gasps )
Then punish me if you have to,
but, sire, I beg you to please
wait until we’ve defeated them.
Meruem: I don’t care.
It’s pointless.
On the contrary, this is a trial
we chimera ants must overcome
if we are to truly continue
our evolution.
( Both gasp )
Meruem: Youpi,
your own emotional instability,
as well
as the traitor’s betrayal,
we must accept them
and move forward.
Humans are a steppingstone
meant to help us attain
the next level of evolution,
the perfect sacrifice.
The remnants of human ego
within us are variables,
as long as we consider them
but a transitional phase
to our final form.
Narrator: The king’s opinion
had completely reversed
following the explosion.
Was this a result of the blast?
No. They were both
part of the king.
Shaiapouf: If the enemy
can become invisible,
I can find him
by making contact.
I need to split myself
into the smallest segments
that can still see
and then expand the search.
Knuckle: Bastard.
I’m not his target.
That much is obvious.
He turned back just like that.
Who is he after?
Is he looking for meleoron,
the traitor?
Because that would be bad.
We have to defeat the king,
but I don’t see how we can
without meleoron’s ability.
I’ve got to protect meleoron,
no matter the cost.
Palm: Pouf divided
his segments to the point
that they’re
too small for me to see.
Unlike his main body,
his segments have to be
at full size for me to see them.
Shaiapouf:
The man with the pompadour
was obviously just a decoy.
They must know that we’ve
made sense of it by now
and we know
the chameleon is a traitor.
In other words, they believe
that’s why i’ve returned,
to dispose
of the double-crosser.
Assuming that the chameleon
is concealing himself
and the others as they flee
and assuming
that the woman is among them,
I can’t get too close.
If I do, they will
protect the chameleon
and abandon her.
I’m certain of it.
They believe
the chameleon is my target.
If they only knew
how wrong they are.
They’d never imagine that I
would return to kill the woman
pitou was trying
so desperately to heal.
If they’re under the impression
that i’ve come back
in order to rescue the woman,
well, that’s even better.
And if i’m lucky, they may even
offer to hand her over to me,
with conditions, of course.
♪
Knuckle: That little monster’s
after meleoron. He must be.
It would make perfect sense,
because, to them, he’s nothing
more than a traitor.
Killua: Hold on.
We need to be sure about it.
( Panel buzzes )
( Segments gasp )
♪
( Breeze blowing )
Shaiapouf: The door
leading underground?
So that’s it.
They’ve realized I know
they can become invisible,
and they’ve decided
to give me two options.
Either the chameleon ran inside,
or he fled
somewhere else entirely.
That’s their plan.
They intend to weaken me
by splitting up my segments
even further.
- ( Segments chattering )
- No. Over there.
- Over there.
- There.
( Shaiapouf gasps )
♪
What?
Shaiapouf:
They’re giving me a choice.
I can either pursue
the traitor or the girl.
( Groans )
So they want to determine
what my target is. Is that it?
What should I do?
Do I split up my segments
to hide my objective,
or do I send the majority
of them after the chameleon
in order to try
and fool the enemy?
Even if the shutters are closed,
I can slip through it if
my segments are particle-sized.
No. There’s no time.
I’ve made my decision.
I’ll go after the girl!
Killua: So she’s his target?
Shaiapouf: I only
have to kill the woman
and hide her body from the king
for a short time.
My segment can manage that.
I only need a minute!
♪
- ( Electricity crackles )
- ( Shaiapouf gasps )
I see.
This boy,
he’s unbelievably fast.
Killua: So she’s
your target, huh?
Well, i’m up for a game of tag,
and I can play all night long.
( Shaiapouf gasps )
Judging by
how quickly he reacted,
it would be nearly impossible
for me to catch him,
even at full strength.
If I don’t hurry,
the king will arrive.
What do I do?
Narrator: Pressured
by the crisis he faced,
pouf came up with an evil plan.
Shaiapouf: That’s it.
I know the perfect magic trick.
( Killua gasps )
He split himself into pieces?
But he won’t be big enough
to take her away.
What’s his plan?
Is he gonna attack me first?
That’s gonna backfire.
You’ve reduced
your speed and power,
which means I don’t need
to use godspeed anymore.
Shaiapouf: Don’t you see
that resistance is futile?
All of your
so carefully laid plans
have already been foiled.
( Killua gasps )
Shaiapouf: Knowing that,
what’s the point in adding
to your transgressions?
If fear of punishment
is driving you to flee,
you needn’t worry.
The king will forgive you.
He is quite a benevolent ruler.
Killua: Don’t make me laugh!
You really think
i’m gonna believe that?!
You’ll probably
just tie me to a tree
and turn me into a soldier.
Komugi: The king?
( Shaiapouf chuckles )
♪
Yes, that’s right.
Keep running,
and don’t stop until you’re
far from the king’s eyes.
Killua: That proves it.
I don’t know why,
but, for some reason,
this girl is
extremely important to the king,
so, for gon and
for the sake of our mission,
I can’t let
the enemy have her.
Komugi: The person chasing us
sounded a lot
like one of the people
who was talking
with dear leader before.
Does that mean the king
is dear leader?
Then who is this,
and who are
all the people he was with?
Shaiapouf: Your twisted
sense of justice is pointless.
You know it will
never benefit the people.
( Komugi murmurs )
Shaiapouf: First,
i’ll put the girl
under my spell.
Then i’ll use magic words
to make her suspicious.
Stop right where you are!
The king and I seek
an open dialogue with you!
Now release the girl,
or face the consequences!
Killua: Bastard.
That’s just a bunch of baloney.
What is he up to?
- Komugi: Let me go.
- ( Killua gasps )
Komugi: Please put me down.
I beg you!
Just let me go! You feel weird!
Killua: Hey! What the hell
are you doing back there?!
Komugi: You’re all staticky,
and I don’t like it!
Killua: What are you
talking about, you idiot?!
I’m trying to save you,
damn it!
Komugi: That’s a lie! ( Grunts )
Killua: Oh, you think so, huh?
You trust that insect
more than you trust me?
Komugi: Insect? What insect?!
What are you talking about?!
( Killua groans ) I forgot.
- Komugi: Let go! Please!
- Killua: She can’t see.
That’s gonna make it
pretty hard to explain.
- Komugi: Just let me go!
- ( Killua gasps )
( Komugi yells )
- ( Heads thump )
- ( Groans )
♪
Shaiapouf: Damn it. Almost.
( Laughs )
It didn’t take long
for the poison to kick in.
If the woman you’re
carrying chooses to resist,
your speed is bound to suffer.
♪
Killua: What’s going on?
He wasn’t aiming for me,
which has to mean
he was aiming for the woman.
He wanted to kill her.
Shaiapouf: If she escapes,
that’s fine.
If she distracts him
with her resistance,
allowing me to kill her,
that’s all the better.
Oh, miss komugi!
The enemies see you
as a valuable hostage!
They will not kill you,
so go on! Keep struggling!
Keep fighting back
against your captors!
I will save you soon!
( Gasps )
♪
Killua: She’s knocked out.
All right, I won’t pretend
to know what your deal is,
but what I do know
is that you’re really
starting to piss me off.
( Electricity crackling )
You step inside this circle...
I’ll kill you.
( Shaiapouf growls )
♪
Killua: It’s true
you might be a segment,
but you were still formed
from the original’s cells,
weren’t you?
I only have to burn them,
and they’ll die.
Shaiapouf: Electricity.
Killua: Come on.
I’ll torch you piece by piece.
( Shaiapouf groans )
Meruem: Are you having trouble?
( Shaiapouf gasps )
Meruem: I can feel
your impatience.
I shall lend you a hand.
Shaiapouf: There’s no need
to concern yourself.
Your priority should be
regaining your memory,
lord meruem.
I’ll take them just as soon
as my body has returned.
Lord meruem, feast your eyes
on the scene before you.
♪
Humans as far as we can see.
Does this refresh your memory?
They are here for you.
Each one of them
belongs to you!
Meruem: They belong to me?
Shaiapouf: You will rule
over these ignorant,
inferior creatures
and stand proudly
atop the food chain!
The entire world will shine
beneath your glorious light.
This is your divine destiny!
♪
Meruem: Something isn’t right.
Shaiapouf: Huh?
Meruem: Something...
Is missing, something important,
something that isn’t this.
( Shaiapouf gasps )
What are you saying, sire?
You must be mistaken.
Nothing could be more important
than ruling over all life forms.
Meruem: Maybe you’re right.
Perhaps the explosion
has left me confused.
However...
The pain won’t cease.
Tell me, why is
the palace in shambles?
Menthuthuyoupi: It was
destroyed during the battle.
It broke out not very long after
you had left the palace, sire.
Meruem: Now then, where do I
spend most of my time?
Shaiapouf: The problem is,
sire, it’s been destroyed.
Meruem: I suppose
I should see what’s left.
Shaiapouf: Of course.
It’s possible
you’ll find something
to help jog
your memory down there.
One can hope.
( Gasping )
This is bad.
That could be it,
the gungi board and pieces.
( Killua gasps )
Shaiapouf: If he sees them,
they’ll trigger his memory.
I must dispose of them,
and quickly!
Killua: He just gave up?
( Wind blowing )
Gon: Over there.
♪
Let’s go.
( Singing in Japanese )