♪
Narrator: The hunters
have entered the palace
in order to exterminate
the chimera ant king.
( Blows striking )
( Menthuthuyoupi gasps )
( A.p.r. Titters )
Menthuthuyoupi:
I guess my attacks
don’t affect it at all.
What is that damn thing?
( Knuckle chuckles )
Menthuthuyoupi:
Don’t run away! Answer me!
What is this?!
Knuckle: You really
think i’d tell you,
you son of a bitch!
If you wanna know,
you gotta catch me!
( Menthuthuyoupi groans )
Narrator:
To spare the injured shoot
and to draw
youpi’s attention to himself,
knuckle began
to taunt him mercilessly.
♪
( Menthuthuyoupi roaring )
Meleoron: Damn! Knuckle’s
planning to fight youpi alone,
and I can’t get to him,
not through that deadly,
swordlike onslaught.
There’s no way!
In that case...
Shoot: No. I can’t pass out,
not now.
If I do,
then hotel rafflesia
will cease to function.
Any minor wound, any injury...
Will surely not be in vain.
( Groaning )
I-I can...
Still keep going.
Meleoron: Right now,
my job isn’t to help him.
( Sobs )
No matter how much I want to!
My job is to use my power
to help the others
to complete the mission
as fast as possible.
Narrator:
Though it broke his heart,
meleoron had to leave
the two hunters
and follow gon and killua
to fulfill his mission.
Meanwhile, ikalgo proceeded
further into the palace
to rescue palm.
( Elevator dings )
Ikalgo: Satellite dragonflies.
Palm is a friend of my friends,
and I will rescue her.
Any friend of theirs
is a friend of mine.
Narrator: Morel was first
to reach the throne room,
and he waited to continue
his battle with pouf,
who remained in his cocoon.
As netero and the king
were leaving the palace,
gon and killua located
their target, neferpitou,
all for the purpose
of avenging their friend kite.
♪
( Singing in Japanese )
Gon: Do you remember who I am?
( Joints creak )
My name is gon freecss!
And I came here for one reason,
to make you restore kite!
♪
Narrator: For pitou,
gon’s words fell on deaf ears.
The only thing on pitou’s mind
was solving this crisis
and carrying out
the king’s orders.
Every cell in pitou’s body was
focused on that singular task.
Neferpitou: I must
protect komugi at any cost.
Killua: Something’s wrong.
Narrator: Killua,
watching closely,
noticed the abnormality.
Killua: The enemy’s
right there in front of him,
so why isn’t he
preparing for battle?
I can’t sense any aura
around them at all.
Pitou’s defenseless,
might as well be
completely naked.
Does pitou think
we’re beatable...
Without using aura?
No, it’s impossible.
Gon has a totally different kind
of aura than before.
Nobody can fight that naked,
not even pitou.
Then is it the distance?
Does pitou think that from here,
if we decide
to launch an attack,
there’ll still be enough time
to activate nen?
It’s possible.
But if that’s the case,
why doesn’t it look that way?
♪
It almost looks like--
that’s it!
This looks like...
( Cat yowls )
A mother shielding her young
with her own body,
protecting the weak
from a predator.
But that’s ridiculous.
No way pitou’s capable of that.
But then...
Why did grandpa say...
Zeno: Killua,
when you get inside,
you make the call.
Killua: Why was he so cryptic?
( Gasps )
Narrator: While killua
struggled desperately
against his own intuition,
gon couldn’t take his eyes
off the girl lying before them,
conjuring images in his mind
of his broken friend kite.
( Rattling )
Gon: Get away from her now.
( Neferpitou gasps )
Gon: I said
step away from her,
and take that monster
with you.
I came here so I could
make kite whole again,
so come and fight me!
( Gasps )
♪
Narrator: Pitou knelt
with palms upturned,
showing that no harm
was intended.
Killua understood immediately.
♪
Neferpitou: Please, just...
Wait a while.
( Gon shudders )
♪
Are you kidding?!
Why the hell
should I wait for you?!
( Panting )
Get up! We’re going outside!
Narrator: Gon needed
an outlet for his rage,
but with pitou being
so unexpectedly submissive,
he had none.
Meanwhile, killua was
starting to understand
what was going on. It was...
Zeno: I know nothing
beyond the mission I was given.
Killua: So what he meant
was that something unexpected
had happened.
Grandpa didn’t know anything
when he brought
the dragons down.
If I had to take a guess,
his mission was probably to use
dragon dive and dragon head
to get the king
and his royal guards
away from each other,
but he didn’t know
she was here, too.
Wait. She must be
the third party,
the one none of us even
knew existed. It’s her!
♪
If i’m right,
then more than likely,
she’s the reason
the king hurt himself.
Why would the king
do something so bizarre?
It must be
because she’s special,
special to the king.
So that’s why pitou
isn’t taking her apart.
Pitou’s healing her
on the king’s orders.
Pitou’s healing ability
doesn’t just preclude using en.
All aura must be focused
on the healing ability
when it’s being used.
Narrator: But as important
as this information was,
killua was painfully aware
that it would only have
a negative effect on gon.
Killua: What do I do?
What should I say?
- Gon!
- Neferpitou: I’ll do anything!
( Gasps )
I’ll do anything
you want me to do,
but you have to wait,
because i--
I have to save this person,
no matter the cost!
♪
Gon: "Save"?
What do you mean
by "save," huh?
Killua: "Anything"?
You say that
you’ll do anything?
Gon: Killua...
I’m asking the questions here.
( Killua gasps )
Gon: What do you mean by "save"?
Tell me.
Narrator: Pitou didn’t know
what to say in this situation,
but what came out was...
Neferpitou:
This girl is precious
to someone I really care about
more than you
could possibly know.
Narrator: The truth,
plain and simple.
Neferpitou: Because of her,
the king became who he is today.
If she ceases to exist, the king
will cease to be who he is.
She means that much, so...
All I want is for her to live.
I beg you to let me heal her,
and then i’ll do
anything you ask of me,
so please just wait.
Gon: You want to save her life?
You’re telling me
that you really...
Want to save this girl’s life?
( Shuddering )
How dare you say that?
( Aura exploding )
How dare you?!
Damn it! Why, you...
Why should I wait?!
Why should I
do anything you say?!
( Neferpitou gasps )
Killua: Gon, just wait a second.
Look, that girl’s really hurt,
probably because of us
and grandpa’s dragon dive.
Gon: And?
Killua: And pitou’s
likely healing her.
Well, that’s what it
looks like, anyway.
Gon: So?
Killua: Hold off.
Wait until it’s done.
Gon: "Likely"? "Probably"?
You want me to wait
because of that?
Even if we did wait,
there’s no way we can guarantee
pitou will follow through
on that promise!
"Probably"? "Likely"?
For real?
The hell with that!
Quit messing around!
( Panting )
What the hell’s
the matter with you?!
You want--
you want me to trust
this thing?! Seriously?!
Because there’s no way in hell!
( Arm cracks )
( Both gasp )
♪
( Chorus vocalizing )
Neferpitou: If you like,
i’ll break my right arm as well,
and if that’s not enough...
Then i’ll break my legs.
( Whimpers )
If you truly think that
I won’t keep my promise
after I heal her,
you can mangle my body
all you want,
as long as it doesn’t
hinder my ability to treat her.
Just let me do that.
Please, i’m begging you.
Please let me save her.
( Gon shuddering )
( Chorus continues )
( Rubble clatters )
Gon: No fair.
It’s not fair, damn it!
Why are you
helping her, anyway?!
After all of the things
that you did to my friend kite!
Killua: Gon!
Gon: Why?!
( Shudders )
I want you to tell me!
( Shuddering )
To hell with this.
( Neferpitou gasps )
Gon: Show me...
Killua: No. You kill pitou,
and kite will never
be whole again.
Gon: Must be real nice for you.
You can stay calm...
Because it’s not your fight.
Killua: I’m only saying this,
because it looks
like you’re losing it.
Did you forget what you told me
in the very beginning?
We’re here to get kite back.
Get it together, damn it!
Gon: Okay.
I’ve calmed down now.
For how long?
How long should we wait?
( Neferpitou gasps )
Uh, I estimate it will take
three to four hours
to heal her completely.
Gon: Sorry. Too long.
( Neferpitou gasping )
Then give me just one hour,
and I can heal
her most critical injuries.
I’m begging you, so please.
Gon: You can have one hour,
and then you’re
coming to peijing,
because you’re gonna heal kite.
Can you promise me that?
Neferpitou: I can.
I promise you.
Gon: I’ll wait right here
for one hour.
( Wind blowing )
♪
( Singing in Japanese )