phinks: Okay,
now let me get this straight.
They can’t avenge them,
because they’re arguing
over whether
they’re dead or altered?
Some things never change.
They always lose sight
of what’s important,
so we’re gonna
do things our way.
If anyone interferes,
we’ll take them down,
as simple as that.
♪
( Singing in Japanese )
( Chorus vocalizing )
( Explosion )
Narrator: Zazan has built
her nest in meteor city.
Calling herself the queen,
she seeks to rule the world.
But there is a group who has
risen to quell her ambitions.
They are natives of this city,
the phantom troupe.
bonolenov:
Where’s everyone else?
Phinks: Beats me. Maybe
they’re still out having fun?
I should have enjoyed myself
instead of obliterating
the opponent. Hmm?
♪
Kalluto: That took
longer than expected.
Nasty habit.
I really need to stop
toying with my prey.
♪
( Zazan laughs )
( Laughs )
You’re just no match for me.
Why don’t you come back when
you’ve gotten your act together?
Feitan: Fair point.
Zazan: My, I must say,
you took that pretty well.
Feitan: It looks like
i’m out of shape.
But it’s a good chance
to practice.
♪
( Shizuku grunting )
( Pike laughing )
( Gasps )
( Sighs )
I’m stuck on defense.
he’s fast
and has twice as many limbs.
I need to create an opening.
Pike: Wait a minute. This again?
Right when I think
it’s finally gone,
that girl somehow manages
to make that stupid vacuum
appear out of nowhere.
So her ability lets her pull out
and store objects at will?
yes, I see now.
That’s very interesting.
hmm, and I can’t seem
to catch her with my gossamer.
This girl is surprisingly good,
but I cannot allow her
to escape my clutches.
I really hate to do this.
It’s so hard on my butt.
But I have no choice!
♪
Love shower!
shizuku: Whoa.
He might have me this time.
( Pike laughs )
With all the silk
I keep spinning,
you’ve got nowhere
to run to now. Lucky me!
( Laughs )
Gotcha!
( Shizuku grunting )
( Pike laughs )
It’s useless!
Even bihorn couldn’t snap
my silk when he tried,
and he’s the strongest
out of all of us, no question!
Now, then, time to hand you over
to mistress zazan.
This is wonderful.
i just hope
she praises me for this.
( Gasps )
It got lighter? Impossible.
( Grunting )
How?
How did she escape my web?!
( Groans )
What the...
Oh.
You took your clothes off.
I get it.
She widened an opening
in my web to slip through
while protecting her skin.
with her power,
it’s certainly feasible.
( Shizuku gasps )
Pike: She left her vacuum
in the web,
but she can make it disappear
and call it back again
once she’s out.
But now your clothes
are already off,
so you can’t use
the same trick again.
Shizuku: Maybe not, but I
could say the same thing to you.
I’ve been able to learn
the range and speed
of your silk.
I won’t mention that his anus
twitches twice before he fires.
i’ll just keep
my distance from now on,
so blinky and I get the win.
Pike: Win? ( Laughs )
Oh, you’re such
a stupid, stupid girl!
You just said you were
gonna run away from here!
Shizuku: I said that i’m going
to be keeping my distance,
not that i’m gonna run away.
Pike: Hmm?
Shizuku: Hold on a sec.
I’ll show you the difference.
- Ready, blinky?
- Blinky: Gyo gyo.
Shizuku: Suck up every last
drop of blood from his body.
Blinky: Gyo gyo!
( Pike gasps ) Hey.
Hold on a second. What?!
♪
Knock it off! Stop that!
You little weakling!
Uh-oh. This is bad.
I’m getting dizzy.
I have to stop the bleeding.
( Gasps )
( Grunts )
( Muffled grunting )
There’s more?
From here and here?
( Gasping )
This is too much!
I can’t cover them all at once!
Shizuku: Well,
of course you can’t.
i gave you
exactly 29 bleeding wounds.
By my current calculations,
even accounting for the fact you
have eight limbs to work with,
it’ll be impossible for you
to plug
each laceration in time,
unless you grow another limb.
There. All cleaned up.
Blinky: Gyo.
Shizuku: Mm?
Mm...
Hey, so you produce
sticky webbing, right?
If you had wrapped it
around yourself,
it would have stopped
the bleeding, wouldn’t it?
Guess we’re both
pretty stupid, huh?
♪
( Somber chorus vocalizing )
Kalluto: Wait. What is this?
How can they move so fast?
Phinks: Looks like
he’s moving better now.
bonolenov: Still not
at the top of his game, though.
( Kalluto grunts )
They were already here
enjoying the fight.
I mean, I know I wasted
some time dallying around,
but I wasn’t slow.
♪
Five? No, seven?
How many feints was that?
And how is he able to leap from
that position while attacking?
( Gasps )
Now he’s over there!
( Gasping )
This is beyond
my comprehension.
They’re on a completely
different level.
♪
shizuku: Whoa.
Everyone’s already here?
( Phinks gasps )
New look?
Shizuku: I got caught up
in my opponent’s webs.
phinks: Are you
really saying you lost?
Shizuku: No, I won.
( Shalnark laughs )
She’s pretty mad, huh?
bonolenov:
It’s down to feitan now.
Shalnark: His opponent’s tough.
Phinks: It’s probably the queen.
Shizuku: But feitan
isn’t moving very well.
Shalnark: He isn’t
back to full power yet.
Kalluto: I know.
You said that already.
I still have far to go.
I lack strength.
♪
Zazan: Behind me?
( Gasps )
What’s with this guy?
He keeps getting faster,
and his friends
are flocking here.
Curse those worthless idiots.
Were they all defeated?
( Feitan chuckles )
Who knew your skin was so tough?
( Zazan growls )
Why, you little--
how dare you scar
my beautiful face?!
( Grunting )
( Panting )
You’re dead!
Feitan: Ko.
She’s leaving herself wide open,
and i’m not nice enough
to overlook that.
( Gasps )
( Kalluto gasps )
But her attack
didn’t make contact.
phinks: No. She threw
some weak aura with that swing.
Feitan’s idea to use ko
just backfired on him.
He focused every last ounce of
his energy into a single point,
and it didn’t do a damn thing,
and that error delayed
his defense by a split second.
in other words,
he left himself defenseless.
That’s why such a crude emission
dealt him such severe damage.
( Feitan gags )
Phinks: She knows how to use
her aura, that’s for sure.
Shalnark: Well, she isn’t
a queen for nothing, you know.
( Zazan laughs )
My body is indestructible!
kalluto:
Shouldn’t we go help him?
Phinks: Huh? Why would we?
I mean, it is a race, isn’t it?
If he loses, that just means
the next person gets to try.
Shizuku: So who’s up next?
Shalnark: Well,
who got here first?
Phinks: That’d be me.
Bonolenov: Wait. We both
arrived at the same time.
Phinks: Oh, give me a break.
I was just waiting
until you finished your fight,
you idiot.
Shalnark: Okay, okay.
Let’s flip a coin.
Kalluto: I-I don’t get it.
What’s wrong with these people?
- Shalnark: It’s heads.
- Bonolenov: Right,
so if feitan goes down,
I get to try next.
( Phinks groans )
Kalluto: I was naive.
I thought I could rise
to number two in no time...
But i’m utterly inferior.
It’s hopeless.
Still, I can’t give up.
I’m used to waiting it out.
♪
I’ll get my brother back,
no matter how long it takes.
( Bone cracks )
Phinks: There goes his left arm.
hey, feitan,
you ready to tag out?
( Feitan spits )
Parc fuh eceip.
( Phinks and shalnark gasp )
Feitan: Kcul ruoy sserp
tndluohs uoy.
Phinks: Damn, run for it.
If you get caught up in this,
you’re dead.
Bonolenov: When feitan snaps,
he’ll lash out
at everything around him.
shizuku: We tried
to watch him once before,
and we almost got killed.
Phinks: His ability
has a pretty wide range
that’s activated by rage,
so he doesn’t hold back.
I’m pretty sure this one
would obliterate you,
and probably instantly.
Kalluto: "This one"?
There are different kinds?
Damn it! I wanna see!
( Chorus vocalizing )
( Gasps )
Zazan: What the...
When did he put that on?
Wait. Never mind that.
He’s much stronger now!
Feitan: Niap eht kcab yap lli.
With scorching heat.
Pain packer!
Zazan: Huh?
( Kalluto panting )
Feitan: Rising sun.
( Zazan screams )
( Both gasp )
( Zazan screaming )
( Feitan speaking backward )
( Laughing )
Zazan: Impossible!
No. I am the queen!
I can’t die here...
Not like this.
( Feitan laughing )
♪
Out of gas already?
and the heat
really wasn’t that bad.
How unfortunate.
If only you had dealt me
more damage,
you’d have had a quicker death.
Well, you only had
yourself to blame.
Phinks: Would you look at that?
It doesn’t seem
like any of them
reverted back to normal
once their queen died.
Shalnark: Maybe not,
but at least none of them
- are under her control anymore.
- Phinks: Hmm?
( Chimera ant groaning )
( Stammering )
K-k-kill me.
Chimera ant #2: Have mercy.
Kill us.
( Phinks scoffs )
Hell, no.
I don’t do mercy killings.
But feel free to attack us.
Where’s your pride?!
you’re still natives
of meteor city, aren’t you?!
What’s the matter with you?!
Show us you got
some fight left!
( Chimera ant #1 grunts )
Phinks: Send yourselves off
in style!
♪
Should have guessed.
Now those geezers are arguing
over whether to expand their
retaliation to the real queen.
Man, i’m getting sick
of those idiots.
They just sit around a table
squawking about things
they can’t even do.
shizuku: Okay,
but we’re not leaving, right?
Phinks: We really don’t have
anything else to do.
If any more of those ants
show up here, i’ll crush them.
Killing survivors like that
left an awful aftertaste.
( Cellphone rings )
Is it the boss?
Shalnark: No, nobunaga.
He’s asking if we’ll go over
and help him with his job.
Phinks: He’s gotta be joking.
No chance in hell! Idiot!
Ah, man. This sucks.
Damn, I hate having to wait.
Shalnark: Wow, you’re starting
to sound just like a girl
with a big crush,
aren’t you, phinks?
Feitan: Girly girl.
Phinks: Huh?
What was that, you bastards?!
Say that again, and you’re dead!
( Feitan laughs )
Shalnark: Hey! Be careful!
We’re injured, you know?!
Narrator: The phantom troupe has
successfully saved meteor city
from the chimera ant invasion.
♪
Meanwhile...
gon and killua
are making preparations
to infiltrate
the Republic of east gorteau.
The selection of citizens
to be presented to the king,
carried out
by his own royal guards...
Will begin in nine days.
♪
( Singing in Japanese )