♪
Referee: Round seven
of the championship finals.
Get ready!
Go!
Both: Show me...
Rock! Jan Ken pon!
Referee:
And the winner is killua!
Killua: Yes!
( Gon groans )
Referee: Very nice.
And now here’s your prize,
the sword of truth.
( Both gasp )
Killua: Whoa.
Hey, check it out, gon.
Card number 83.
It goes in a specified slot.
Gon: All right! One card down.
Both: Score!
♪
( Singing in Japanese )
Gon: The problem is, how are
we gonna protect the card?
Killua: Well, we don’t have
any defensive spell cards,
so we should probably get some.
- Man: Wait!
- Both: Hmm?
Man: Yeah, you kids!
H-hand over
the sword of truth right now.
Look, I don’t
wanna have to rough you up,
so just do what I tell you.
Killua: No way, you idiot.
Man: Hey, hold on! Book!
Gon: Book!
Player: Ha!
You’re bluffing, right?
I already know
that you just started
playing the game
a little while ago.
You’re both newbies,
so you haven’t obtained
any defensive spells yet,
except for the sword of truth.
This is thief.
This spell card lets you
steal one random card
from another player’s
specified slots.
Take this! Thief on!
Attack killu--
eh?
Gon: Haven’t you
trained at all, mister?
Nice try.
I won’t give it back
the next time.
Killua: You must be an amateur.
This is a game for pro hunters.
I’m impressed
that you even made it in.
( Player groans )
Killua: But at least
we learned something.
An attack spell won’t kick in
until you finish the chant.
Player: Yeah,
but a strategy like that
only works
on the very weakest players!
Player #2: Exactly.
( Both gasp )
Player #2: If you want a card,
you just take it
from someone else.
Only fools actually participate
in tournaments.
Understand, boys?
If not, you will.
Gon: They really piss me off!
Killua: Just forget it.
Those guys were all pros.
At least
they didn’t use brute force.
Gon: Damn it! Then i’ve really
gotta start focusing hard
on building up my spell cards.
Killua: In that case,
I say we should head out
to masadora, the city of magic.
Gon: Sounds like a plan.
( Girl giggles )
( Birds squawk )
♪
Player: That’s our hideout.
We’re gonna start off
by assigning roles.
Everyone here right now
will be collecting
spell cards for us.
You’ve probably heard there are
40 different spell cards.
We need you to obtain one,
fortress.
This is one of the strongest
defensive spells in existence,
and we could certainly use
another one of those.
It will help us
to protect angel’s breath.
Puhat: And what the hell
is angel’s breath?
Player: It’s a super-rare card
with an ss rank
that no one has ever been able
to get their hands on.
Player #2: How can you be sure
no one’s ever obtained it?
Player #3: There’s a spell card
called list.
Casting it tells you the current
conversion number of one card
as well as the number of people
who have it.
Puhat: Yeah, okay.
Player #3: The card is
incredibly difficult to obtain,
because you need
to have all 40 spell cards
in your possession
before you can trade for one.
Of course, spell cards are
extremely useful in this game,
so players tend to use them up.
Player #1: But now,
after a whole lot of searching
we’ve completed our collection
of all 40 spell cards.
What we’d like to do
is trade them in
for an angel’s breath card
right now, but...
Player #2: If you did,
you’d have nothing
to protect it with.
That’s why you need a copy
of the fortress, correct?
Player #1: Exactly.
That said,
in order for this plan to work,
what we want you to do
is to make a complete list
of the 40 spell cards
and commit them to memory.
Killua: Those four
gargaider cards got us 120,000.
Gon: I know.
They were pretty valuable.
We don’t need to worry
about money now.
Hey, why don’t we buy
some food and water?
Then we’ll head to masadora.
Killua: Sure,
but first we need a map.
The one with information
costs 650,000,
and the blank one’s only 20.
Which do you want?
Gon: The blank one!
That way, we get all the fun
of filling it in ourselves.
Killua: You’re so positive,
it’s painful.
Gain.
( Map beeping )
Wow, this doesn’t
tell us anything.
Gon: Let’s ask for directions.
Shopkeeper:
Head north for 80 kilometers.
After you pass by the mountain,
you’ll get to a lake.
You’re gonna want to follow that
lake north for a little while,
and it’ll take you
right to masadora.
Killua: If we hurry, we can do,
like, 80 kilometers a day.
Shopkeeper: Assuming
that you survive, of course.
That mountain is practically
crawling with bandits.
Even worse,
after you pass the mountain,
you’ll encounter
hordes of monsters.
Killua: There’s bandits?
Gon: And monsters?
Killua: Now it’s starting
to sound like an rpg.
Gon: Let’s see what the monsters
look like! Come on! Hurry!
All right! Move out!
Girl: Wait, please!
Um, i’m begging you!
Killua: For what?
I’d really like to join you
if you don’t mind.
Killua: Uh, no way. Sorry.
( Girl gasps )
But may I ask why not?
Killua: You’d slow us down.
Girl: How dare
you speak to me that way,
you little brat?
I could take you out
with one hand tied
behind my back if I wanted to.
That does it.
I was only planning to mess
with them for a little while,
but now i’m going
to completely ruin their lives!
Hey! Hold it right there!
I mean, please?
I’ll try really hard not
to get in your way. I promise.
( Map beeping )
Shalnark: Okay. I have most
of the information we need.
Shizuku: Then can you
tell us what you’ve found?
Shalnark: Mm, of course.
I’ll start with number one.
Shalnark: I tried a hundred
different people in this city,
and they all gave
the same response
when faced
with an unusual question.
That’s typical behavior
for non-playable characters.
Number two, book.
This copy is real,
and this one’s
a copy kortopi made.
Gain.
Kortopi’s didn’t transform.
I believe that might indicate
that the game’s program
didn’t recognize kortopi’s card.
And three, shizuku’s vacuum
seems to function normally
in this world,
but it won’t work on any items
that have special abilities
of any kind.
I think that’s because
the game was programmed
to prevent nen abilities from
being used to collect cards.
Kortopi: I see.
Shizuku: So?
Shalnark: However,
these three points
indicate
yet another possibility...
This game isn’t taking place
in a virtual world,
it’s based
somewhere in the real world.
Shizuku: But what do you mean?
Shalnark: You see,
if any of the players
were to actually enter
"greed island,"
then their souls would
fully detach from their bodies
and enter the console,
leaving their bodies behind.
Sending them in physically
wouldn’t be necessary.
And while separating body
and soul might be possible,
it would take a lot more
than standing in front
of a console and using hatsu.
It would make a lot more sense
if the players
were actually teleported
somewhere else entirely.
Therefore the software
operating the console
has nothing to do
with playing the game.
Its job is to teleport players
who trigger it with hatsu
to this island.
Shizuku: That stands to reason,
but I don’t think
I get what it means.
Shalnark: The big reward
for clearing the game,
you remember it?
Shizuku: Let’s see. What was it?
Kortopi: Of all the cards you’ve
found for your specified slots,
you can choose three
and take them all back
to the real world with you.
Shalnark: That’s right,
and that means
that every one of these items
are available to be used
outside of the island.
If this game does indeed
take place in the real world,
then it should be possible
to remove all of the treasure
without actually
having to clear the game.
Kortopi: Understood.
Shalnark: Book.
So, at the moment,
we only know a little bit
about a few select items.
It would be most beneficial
to learn about all the cards.
To start, we need the spell card
called eye of god.
And then we just need
to find phinks and feitan.
( Phinks scoffs )
Another cheap map, huh?
Feitan: Still, he was carrying
a lot of spell cards.
Phinks: Well,
wanna split up for now?
Let’s meet back in masadora
in a week.
We’ll see which one of us
can kill more players,
make it a race.
Feitan: Okay, but be sure
to take their cards first.
♪
Gon: So what do you think
we should do about her?
Killua: Just ignore her.
We’ll have a chance to ditch her
once the bandits show up.
Gon: But isn’t that
kind of mean?
Killua: What are you
talking about?
She passed, right?
So she’s got
strong nen abilities.
She can escape if it gets rough.
She’s keeping up better
than I thought she would.
Girl: Their stamina
isn’t half bad,
well, for a couple
of brats, anyway.
( Gasps )
( Both gasp )
Killua: You ready?
Gon: Mm-hmm.
Bandit: Please help us!
We beg you!
- ( Both gasp )
- ( Bandits coughing )
( Insects chirping )
( Boy panting )
Man: The disease is spreading.
( Coughs )
It starts with a mild fever,
but then it gets
progressively worse and worse
until the afflicted
finally dies. ( Coughs )
Elder: All we can
do is use medicine
to keep the fever at bay.
( Coughs )
Sadly, the medicine
only works for about a week.
( Coughs )
Man: It’s also
incredibly expensive,
and now--( Coughs )
We’re completely out of money.
( Coughs )
We’re all sick. ( Coughs )
So we can’t even steal
what we need
like we normally would.
( Coughing )
Gon: Could we catch it?
Killua: It’s probably
just part of the game play.
Man: Help us!
My son only has two
or three more days to live!
Elder: Would you be so kind
as to give us some money?
Every little bit helps.
Gon: So this is part
of the game, too, right?
Killua: Yeah. If we just give
them the right amount of money,
then they’ll probably reward us
with some good items
or some information.
Gon: So, uh, how much
do you guys need?
Elder: 80,000 Jenny.
( Coughs )
Gon: But that’s
all the money we have.
Killua: Yeah.
It sounds like they know
everything about us,
doesn’t it?
Girl: Excuse me,
but I have enough
to cover the 80,000 Jenny.
Killua: Excuse me. We’re busy,
so shut up for a minute.
Girl: I’m gonna kill that brat.
Gon: Okay, we got it.
We’ll give you the 80,000 Jenny.
Elder: You really will?
Man: Thank you both so much!
You’ve just saved
my poor son’s life.
Boy: I-i’m so cold,
so very cold
( man gasps ) This is awful.
If his body gets
even a little bit colder,
he’s going to die before we
can get the medicine into him.
If only we had
some children’s clothes for him.
Why don’t we have clothes?!
Gon: Um...
I guess I could give him
what i’m wearing.
( Man gasps ) Can you, really?
Elder: You’re just like angels
sent to us from heaven.
Mere words
aren’t nearly sufficient...
Man: To express the depths
of our gratitude!
Gon: Oh, no need to thank us.
Killua: Unless you’ve
got items or info.
Both: Hmm?
Killua: We got nothing!
Gon: We gave
all of our clothes away,
and now we’re
totally broke, too!
Killua: Damn it!
They’re messing with us.
Girl: I wonder
what that was all about.
Gon: But as soon
as we get past this mountain,
we’ll find lots
of monsters, right?
Killua: Yeah.
If we beat a few of ’em
and turn ’em into cards,
we can sell them for cash!
Gon: And then we might
finally get to start fighting!
Killua: Time to see
what you’ve got.
Gon: You, too!
I wanna see
what you’ve accomplished
in your secret training.
I can’t wait!
♪
Gon: This area’s really rocky.
Killua: Let’s go for it!
Gon: Yeah!
( Both yell )
Gon: Whoa!
There are tons of ’em!
( Cyclops grunts )
Killua: Gon’s attack
didn’t do anything?
I guess punches
aren’t gonna do it.
And there are so many.
To disable one
with a single attack...
( Cyclops #2 roars )
Killua: Bingo!
We go for the eye!
Book.
Gon, just aim for the eye!
Gon: I got it!
( Cyclops #1 roars )
( Strike lands )
( Cyclops roars )
Girl: Hmm. They’re
moving around way too much,
but otherwise, not bad.
Killua: Mm, they were weaker
than they looked.
Gon: Yeah, but after
we left it alone for a minute,
the card reverted.
Killua: We can
do this easy, gon.
Every one of these monsters
comes with a built-in weakness.
Just gotta stay calm and think.
All right!
Now let’s head for masadora.
Gon: Yeah!
♪
( Chuckles )
( Both scream )
( Both sigh )
- ( Gon grunts )
- Killua: Gon!
Gon: I’m okay.
See? It didn’t even hurt.
This one’s pretty weak.
Killua: Yeah,
but it’s really fast!
Let’s hurry up and catch it!
♪
Damn it!
( Gon grunts )
( Girl sighs )
Aim where it’s going to be.
If you watch closely,
you can learn
an opponent’s pattern of motion.
Your eyes are sharp, but you
aren’t using them properly.
Gon: It got away from us.
Killua: You know, if the rest
of the monsters are this weak,
we’re gonna get to masadora
in no time.
Girl: Ugh. Don’t be so stupid.
What if you encounter one
that’s strong and fast?
( Hoofbeats )
Both: Hmm?
( Creature neighs )
Gon: Are those bubbles?
( Grunts )
Killua: It’s gone.
It’s loud,
and it generates a shock wave,
but there’s no real damage.
Gon: The red ones don’t pop
when you touch ’em.
Girl: Actually
the white bubbles pop
when they make contact
with a human’s aura.
The red ones pop when they
make contact with anything else.
To catch that horse, you must
identify which bubble is which
and then switch smoothly
between zetsu and ten.
Unfortunately that’s still
too difficult for them.
Still, these boys are--
they’re...
They’re just...
Wasting their potential!
They’re rough gemstones
that will shine
with just a little polishing!
But at this rate,
they’ll run into
stronger players or monsters,
and it’ll be game over!
♪
( Armor sighs )
Gon: Now this one
looks a lot tougher.
Girl: That’s it!
I’ve had enough.
Gyo!
- Gon: Huh?
- Killua: Hmm?
Girl: Keep your eyes on it!
Use gyo! You know how, don’t ya?
See? The armor’s just a puppet!
Attacks aren’t going to work
against it!
( Armor sighs )
Gon: Here it is!
( Creature squeals )
Gon: Look. I got the card.
Girl: So you guys can use gyo.
Then why didn’t you
use it before, huh?
Killua: Uh, well, I...
Gon: Yeah.
Girl: You forgot, didn’t you?
Both: Huh?
Girl: Don’t just stand there!
Gyo!
Tell me what you see.
Both: The number one.
Girl: Very good. Now listen up.
When I raise my finger,
I want you to use gyo.
Then yell out whatever it is
you see, all right?
The same applies if you
sense anything suspicious.
Use gyo, got it?
Killua: And what makes you think
you can order us around?
Gon: I see the number five!
Girl: Correct.
You, give me 200 push-ups.
Killua: Huh?!
Girl: It’s your punishment.
Get to it!
Killua: Hey, what the hell?!
Why should I?
Girl: Got a problem?
Killua: Yeah, you bet I do!
Just who do you think
you are, huh?
Girl: I forgot.
I should introduce myself.
See, i’m a pro hunter.
The name is biscuit krueger,
and 40 years ago,
I learned nen,
and now i’m going to use
my knowledge and experience
to give you
some much-needed coaching.
You should both
be eternally grateful.
Gon: You learned nen
40 years ago?!
Killua: You’re just a hag!
♪
Narrator: As luck would have it,
the young girl
following gon and killua
is actually a veteran
professional hunter.
Biscuit: Hmph.
( Singing in Japanese )