Genthru: I’m going
to crush his spirit,
his will to fight,
to stand, and to resist.
I’ll make him see.
I’ll prove to him that all
his hard work and confidence
mean absolutely nothing.
♪
( Singing in Japanese )
( Birds squawk )
( Gon gasps )
So fast.
There’s no way to parry.
But I can still defend
against it.
Genthru: Hmm. Gyo, huh?
The moment I grasped his arm,
he focused his aura there
to block my attack.
( Groans )
You fool.
You think you’ve
figured me out now, don’t you?
( Gon gasps )
( Gasping )
Genthru: Aw, what’s the matter?
That was just
a simple body blow.
If you focus your aura
wherever I grab you,
then you leave yourself open
everywhere else.
Pointless.
In fact,
it was worse than pointless.
It even backfired on you.
( Gon laughs )
Genthru: Eh?
It’s just like bisky said.
Genthru: Hmm.
You won’t be smiling
much longer!
( Blows whooshing )
One more, and you’re finished.
- ( Gon grunts )
- ( Genthru gasps )
Impossible.
That was the hardest hit so far.
He shouldn’t have
been able to counter,
but he did, and that means
that he kept the damage
to a minimum.
In other words, he blocked me
with standard defenses,
not by relying on aura.
Did he just guess that I
wouldn’t set off an explosion?
No. That look.
Gon: So, hey, bisky,
how come genthru doesn’t get
burned by his own explosions?
Bisky: Oh,
it’s pretty simple, actually.
You see, he covers his hand
with more aura
than he uses to detonate.
Gon: Oh, I get it.
Bisky: It’s a technique
that requires
quite a large reserve of aura.
Now’s as good a time as any.
Let’s see if you can tell, huh?
Excellent reaction.
You’ve almost perfected gyo.
All right, now one more time.
Gon: Huh?
Bisky: You could tell
the difference?
Gon: Yeah. You used less aura
the second time, didn’t you?
Bisky: Yes, that’s right.
You pass!
Now that you can tell
the difference,
you’re going to have
a much easier time facing him.
Right before genthru
uses his little flower,
he’ll use gyo on his hand,
but when he’s
pretending to use his ability,
he’s going to attack you
somewhere else
- and won’t bother using gyo.
- Gon: Ah.
Bisky: If you can feel
whether the hand touching you
is protected by gyo or not,
that means you’ll be able
to thwart his attacks
and feints to some extent.
Genthru: I see.
You knew from my gyo.
Very clever.
♪
Like I said before...
The shallow strategy
you’re using,
it’s going to backfire.
If my little flower catches you
when you’re not using enough
aura to defend yourself,
a hit to the face
will blow your eyes,
your nose,
and your mouth clean away.
A hit to the arms or legs
will incinerate your skin,
severely damaging
any nerves or muscle.
You’ll have
no fingers or toes left.
It’s impossible for you to guard
against all of my gyo attacks
with your gyo.
So now what?
I’ve no interest
in continuing this.
This fight
has shown me something.
You have talent,
as well as a promising future
filled with opportunities.
Don’t you think
that throwing it all away
just for the sake of pride
is meaningless?
Come on, brat. Give up already.
Bisky: If he shows signs
that he’s going to use
both hands to blow you up,
that’s a red flag,
and you must focus
on following the plan exactly.
Gon: Biscuit, killua...
I’m sorry.
I know it’s selfish of me,
but i’ve gotta go with my gut.
I have to try, because...
I just had a great idea.
Well, if you
really feel that way,
then just give up, genthru!
♪
Genthru: How unfortunate.
Let me show you
that there are some fates
even worse than dying.
I’ll give you an example.
First, i’ll blow up
both of your arms.
Use gyo to protect
the one you want to keep.
And after that’s done,
i’ll blow up your remaining arm
along with your left leg.
Again, use gyo to protect
the one you want to keep.
We’ll continue in that fashion
until you’re out of limbs.
Yeah, well,
just go ahead, and try!
Genthru: All right.
Take this!
( Gasps )
What--what just happened?
( Gags )
Blood?
I’m injured? Was I attacked?
Gon: Show me rock!
Genthru: Crap.
Move. Get out of the way!
Gon: Jan, Ken...
Rock!
( Winces )
Genthru: Did he hit me?
No. I just tripped.
What the hell was that?
What happened?
( Gasps )
Wait. Now I get it.
This little brat...
Sacrificed both hands!
( Chorus vocalizing )
But it seems the damage
wasn’t distributed evenly.
He probably gave up
on his left hand.
He protected his right
with 30% of his aura
and focused the remaining
70% in his legs to attack me.
I use aura to blow up targets
as well as to shield my hand
from the blast,
but if I attack
with both hands,
it leaves the rest
of my body defenseless.
He took advantage of that.
Still, no sane person
would ever actually try it.
Gon: At least I gave him
a pretty good scare.
( Groaning )
This hurts so bad,
I feel like i’m gonna die,
but i’m going for it.
( Gasps )
That’s...enough.
Genthru: Wait. Is he giving up?
Of course. It all makes sense.
He’s lost his left hand,
and his right is badly injured.
He did manage
to land a hit on me.
Perhaps that satisfied him.
Gon: Okay, i’m done
being selfish now.
( Genthru gasps )
Gon: Time to get serious!
Come on, and fight me!
Genthru: What is wrong
with this brat?
He’s completely insane.
♪
Gon: Book!
( Genthru gasps ) A card?
He shouldn’t have anything
I need to worry about.
Wait. It transformed?
Paladin’s necklace?
What is he planning?
Gon: This is your last chance
to surrender.
Once I use this, you could die,
so think about it carefully.
Genthru: It’s obvious
that you’re bluffing.
But wait. This is my chance.
Book.
I give up.
You’re never
going to admit defeat.
That much is clear.
Take what you want.
I’ll silence him.
Crushing his windpipe and
knocking him out would be best.
Then I can take the cards
from his binder.
- But I do have one request.
- Gon: What?
Genthru: I only ask that you
leave me this card right here.
( Gon gags )
Genthru: He blocked
my second attack with gyo.
But at least I managed
to crush his throat,
which means he won’t be able
to say, "book,"
or, "gain," anymore.
Gon: Genthru...
That’s the worst decision
you could have possibly made.
One minute.
♪
Genthru: That smell.
He can’t use
his little flower anymore.
I’m gonna take him down.
Genthru: Book.
( Laughs )
Oh, I see. This is gasoline.
That’s a good one.
It’s true that I can’t
use little flower now.
However I have
another ability, countdown.
You may recall that I
can set a bomb on someone,
and all I have to do
is touch them
and say the word "bomber."
And if you intend to disarm it,
then your only recourse
would be to touch me
while saying,
"I caught the bomber."
This one is ten times stronger
than little flower,
so you won’t be able
to block it with nen.
All of the activation
requirements have been met.
If I touch you
and say, "bomber,"
the countdown will begin.
I’d run if I were you,
well, if you
still have the strength.
Gon: Oh, yeah? My requirements
have been met, too.
( Raspy )
Now show me rock.
( Genthru gasps )
His earlier attack.
I can’t get too close.
Is he keeping me back?
Gon: Jan, Ken...
Rock!
( Genthru gasps ) A pit trap?
But why? He’s falling, too.
It’s deep,
far too deep to climb out.
Still,
he’s in the same position.
Doesn’t he see
that he’s cornered himself?
( Gasps )
He’s gone.
Gon: Genthru.
( Genthru gasps )
( Gasps )
♪
Gon: If a card is removed
from the binder for a minute,
it reverts to an item.
( Genthru gasps ) A rock?!
( Birds squawking )
( Panting )
Gon: Show me rock.
( Genthru gasps )
Gon: Jan, Ken...
Genthru: No, wait! Hold on!
I surrender! I surrender!
Gon: Rock!
( Genthru gags )
( Gon sighs )
Osu!
Killua: You awake?
Hurry, and get your binder out.
Bisky: That’s right.
We want you to return
all the cards you stole
from the people you betrayed.
Genthru: On one condition.
Use angel’s breath to heal bara
of his injuries.
We have a clone card.
Killua: Don’t worry about it.
That was always
a part of the plan.
Bisky: We already prepared
six copies of clone
for just such an occasion.
( Genthru gasps )
( Sighs )
Book.
( Binder pops )
Bisky: Gain!
♪
Angel: What manner of aid
do you wish of me?
Killua: We need you
to heal his throat
and, while you’re at it,
both of his hands, too.
Scratch that. Just fix
everything wrong with him.
Angel: That is a simple task,
and so I shall restore his body
to its former state.
( Exhales )
( Gon gasps )
- Killua: Whoa!
- ( Bisky laughs )
Gon: Yes! I’m healed!
( Laughing )
Angel: Now fare thee well.
Bisky: Right! Here it is,
the extra angel’s breath card.
Gon: Gain!
( Angel’s breath exhales )
Bisky: Next up is killua.
Okay, genthru, we’re going
to use your binder now.
Genthru: Do as you please.
Bisky: And clone on!
Binder: Attention.
Angel’s breath has reached
its maximum card limit.
The clone will be destroyed.
( Bisky gasps )
Hey, wait a minute!
What just happened?
Did I mess it all up?
Killua: No. It’s goreinu.
He used either clone
or transform
to increase the number
of angel’s breath vouchers.
Two of his vouchers
became angel’s breath.
That must be why.
( Binder chimes )
Attention. Another player
has used contact to reach you.
Goreinu: Hey! It’s goreinu.
Looks like you did it, huh?
But I don’t approve.
If you use angel’s breath
to heal these murderers,
then the trade is off.
Killua: Could I use it?
Goreinu: Yeah, of course.
Killua: But i’m an assassin.
Goreinu: Eh?
Killua: Sure, they’ve killed.
I’ve killed more.
♪
Killua: Every player
in this game
risks their life
in one way or another.
That doesn’t mean
it’s okay to kill people.
But all the people I killed
weren’t nearly as ready to die
as the ones these guys did.
I’m way worse
than they could ever be.
Goreinu: You’re wrong.
You’re not at all like them.
I mean, I like you,
but these guys,
I hate their guts.
Killua: Yeah,
that isn’t very logical.
Goreinu: Oh, forget logic.
It’s how I feel.
Don’t you feel the same way?
Bisky: But it’s
not our place to judge.
We don’t think it’s right
to let them die
just because we hate them.
Both sides
risk their lives in battle,
and both are prepared
to kill if necessary,
but when the fight’s over, well,
those rules cease to apply.
Gon: I still
haven’t forgiven genthru
for killing all those other
players, not yet, at least,
but before the fight
even started,
the three of us agreed
we’d bring six clone cards
with us just in case.
I don’t really remember
why we decided that,
but I do know one thing.
It wasn’t based
on logic or reason.
It just made sense to all of us.
Once the fight was over
and we’d obtained
the angel’s breath card,
we would use it
on whoever was hurt.
We made the decision together,
so we wanted to stick to it,
but I get how you feel,
Mr. Goreinu.
Guess it can’t be helped.
Sorry, killua.
Could you wait a little longer?
Killua: Not a problem.
My hands will eventually heal
on their own.
Gon: Things have changed,
so we can’t use clone anymore,
and there’s just
one angel’s breath left.
Goreinu: Hang on. Only one?
Are you talking
about the original card?
Sub: I want you
to use it on genthru.
( Genthru gasps )
Sub: I’m gonna be all right.
( Angel’s breath exhales )
Killua: Right. Let’s use
accompany to go to masadora.
Gon: Yeah.
Goreinu: Hey, wait up!
All right, you can have
angel’s breath,
whatever you guys want.
( All gasp )
Gon: Really? You’re sure?
Goreinu: Well, to be honest,
even before you
told me everything,
i’d decided to give it to you,
and not just angel’s breath,
but all the cards
that we gathered in the game.
( All gasp )
Goreinu: We all agreed,
tsezguerra, his team, and me.
Thing is, we all decided
to quit the game.
Killua: Oh, wow. I’m all better!
Gon: So Mr. Battera...
Goreinu: Yeah,
he paid off team tsezguerra
for breaking the contract.
I settled
for four billion Jenny.
Bisky: Wait! Four billion?!
You better fork
some of that over now!
Goreinu: Whoa,
what are you talking about?
Of course you get some.
We each get a billion.
( Bisky groans )
( All gasp )
Goreinu: It’s only fair.
I could never
have done this on my own.
It was only possible,
because we all teamed up
and worked together.
( Bisky whimpers )
I can’t believe
what i’m hearing.
You’re a really nice guy!
Has anyone ever told you that?
Goreinu: Anyway,
you can take all the cards.
They’re yours.
But there is one condition.
You must be the first players
to complete the game.
- ( Gon grunts )
- Killua: Piece of cake.
Goreinu: You’ve got
99 specified-slot cards.
That means all you need now
is number zero.
Gon: One more card to go.
Killua: Yeah.
♪
Gon: 97, 98,
and this one makes...
99.
( Binder chimes )
( All gasp )
Woman: This announcement
is for all players.
One of your fellow competitors
has just collected
99 specified-slot cards,
so in honor
of this accomplishment,
ten minutes from now,
we’ll hold
an islandwide quiz contest.
You are all are welcome
to participate if you so choose.
There will be
100 total questions
that deal with
the specified-slot cards.
Whichever player
is able to answer
the most questions correctly
will receive number zero,
ruler’s blessing, as a prize.
Please stand by with
your binders open and ready.
Gon: All the questions are
about the specified-slot cards?
Killua: I get it.
I bet the questions are designed
so that players who mainly stole
their cards can’t answer them.
( Both gasp )
Killua: Someone’s coming.
Bisky: Wait. There are more.
♪
Narrator: The battle
has been long and grueling,
but now it’s reached
the final stage.
( Singing in Japanese )