( Neferpitou gasps )
( Footsteps echoing )
Just stay back.
Don’t come any closer.
Pouf, please.
♪
( Shaiapouf scoffs )
( Singing in Japanese )
♪
Shaiapouf: May I ask why?
If only you had kept quiet,
I would have been able
to kill him quite easily.
Where is all this
irrational fear coming from?
Neferpitou: He noticed you.
If you had closed in
with blood lust,
he would have attacked komugi.
That much, i’m absolutely sure.
That risk was one
I just couldn’t take.
Shaiapouf: I don’t understand.
He’s only sitting there,
because he wants to help
that girl, right?
You almost make it sound
like he intends to harm her,
but why would he do that?
Gon: This is none
of your business.
You just shut up.
( Electricity crackling )
Killua: Once i’m charged up,
i’m heading back to gon.
You go see how knuckle’s doing.
Pouf has moved
outside the barrier now,
so it’s a possibility
the big guy was taken out.
Gauge the situation,
and then decide with knuckle
whether to fight or retreat.
Meleoron: Wait.
What about you guys?
Killua: Once gon gets like this,
he’s not gonna budge
for anything.
I might go down with him.
( Meleoron sighs )
Killua: I’m kidding!
Look, we’re okay.
I’ve got the magic word "kite"
as backup. Don’t worry.
So just leave it to me.
Meleoron: Are you sure?
( Thinking ) But,
if that’s the case, then why...
Why did you look
so sad back there?
You’re positive, right?
Can’t you tell me?
Don’t you want to?
I can’t ask, and I won’t.
Gon: This is none
of your business.
You just shut up.
Shaiapouf: "Just shut up"?
♪
( Wind blowing )
Ah, i’m downwind.
( Chuckles ) You don’t need me.
I’ll go. You’re more than
capable of handling this one.
Farewell.
Gon: Don’t move.
Stay right there.
You use your butterfly wing
scales to control people, right?
Don’t move a step.
♪
Neferpitou: Pouf, please stay.
Shaiapouf: Are you insane?
You want me to stay
and do nothing at all,
just for the sake of that girl?
Neferpitou: It’s for the king.
Please do as he says.
Shaiapouf: What happened here?
Your attitude is completely
different than it was before.
Something happened
while I was imprisoned.
What could it have been?
I give you my word
that I will not move
from this spot, all right?
And all I ask in return
is that you just fill me in
on all that’s happened.
( Thinking )
If I ask where the king is,
he’ll become suspicious
and silence us.
Give me a hint,
something subtle...
And of course try
to make it sound natural.
If you fail, it will be
nothing less than a bloodbath.
That’s all there is to it.
( Neferpitou gasps )
A.p.r.: It is time.
You’ve accrued interest.
( Click )
♪
Menthuthuyoupi:
I’ve got it down.
I know the sensation
of controlling the explosion.
If I do it one more time,
i’ll have it mastered for sure.
I need rage.
I need to feel it again
before I forget!
You made a fool out of me
not once, but twice!
You’re garbage, scum,
pieces of crap!
Calmly release my fury,
destruction
and creation together...
Manifest it throughout my body.
Narrator: As of yet,
youpi had not been able to fully
comprehend the existence
of reciprocal emotions.
And now, in his present state...
Menthuthuyoupi: Rage like this
should never be allowed
to flow freely.
It’s meant to be directed,
to be used!
( Laughs )
I’ll destroy you all!
( Gallops )
( Laughs ) Another fake?
Well, okay!
That’s fine with me!
More! More! Fuel my rage!
Come on!
A.p.r.: It is time.
You’ve accrued interest.
Narrator: A.P.R.’s interest
was calculated
assuming that aura consumption
would continue to rise
at the current rate.
Even if youpi
were to reduce his aura usage
to a bare minimum, in another
three minutes and 50 seconds,
he would lose his nen abilities.
( Morel panting )
Ten left.
( Gasps )
It’s the 11th hour.
I get the feeling
that he’s saving me for last.
If that’s the case,
then i’ll keep fighting
for as long as I can.
Narrator: Morel had deployed
all of his puppets
within youpi’s sight in order
to keep better track of him,
but there was another reason
for this strategy.
His energy
was beginning to wane.
He was so worn out, in fact,
that dispersing them
over a wider area
had become
completely impossible.
If he lost his focus,
the puppets would
turn to smoke and vanish.
Morel: It shouldn’t
be much longer.
He has to run out of nen
at some point, but...
No matter how hard I try,
my body and soul
refuse to move. Damn it.
Narrator: As he summoned
every last ounce of willpower,
morel knew his body would
eventually cease to respond.
Unfortunately, this came sooner
than youpi’s bankruptcy.
Morel: I’m completely out.
Menthuthuyoupi: I’ve got
something I wanna say to you.
Narrator: Youpi, having learned
to compartmentalize his rage,
was finally able
to clear his head.
( Menthuthuyoupi chuckles )
You look like a half-dead fly.
Even so...
You guys are amazing.
♪
Narrator: He had shown
astonishing growth
during combat,
far beyond morel and the others,
but when he spoke,
it was not to taunt
or gloat over his opponent.
Instead, his words
were of pure admiration.
Given morel’s
initial impression of youpi,
this must have been
the very last thing
he expected to hear
in this situation,
but youpi’s feelings
were heartfelt and sincere,
a fact that morel
had no choice but to accept.
Menthuthuyoupi: I’m not
really sure how to say this,
but because you were
so incredible,
I should kill you now.
It’s only proper.
( Morel gasps )
It’s game over.
Menthuthuyoupi:
Well, i’ll put you
out of your misery now,
so don’t move.
Morel: I’m okay
with this right now.
In the end,
he was a worthy adversary.
Menthuthuyoupi: Farewell.
( Wind blowing )
( Morel groans )
Menthuthuyoupi: He’s gone?
Blood.
What’s going on?
Did he teleport?
♪
I was just about
to cut through him
when, all of a sudden,
he disappeared.
I figured one of them
had the ability
to use teleportation,
but when he vanished,
I didn’t see anyone else around.
And I struck
before he disappeared,
so if he did teleport,
I wouldn’t have drawn any blood.
If I could cut him,
why can’t I see him?
Does that mean he’s invisible?
Is that his ability?
No. If it was...
He would have used it
much sooner,
which means
that one of the others
must be able to make
himself invisible,
along with the rest of them,
and right before I stabbed
the guy with the sunglasses,
he stepped in and saved him.
Well, I left a deep wound.
♪
Meleoron: Damn!
The blood.
Youpi can see the blood.
We may be invisible,
but we’re leaving a trail.
If he swings that blade again,
i’ll have no choice
but to get away by myself.
( Gasps ) I can’t hold
my breath any longer.
Damn it.
( Muffled grunting )
Knuckle?
Why did you show yourself?
The plan was for you to stay
hidden as long as possible.
What the hell were
you thinking, you idiot?!
Knuckle: I’m all done
running away and hiding.
I’ll take you on.
( Wind blowing )
So...
Please show them mercy,
all right?
♪
Narrator: Knuckle took a chance
on using diplomacy
instead of violence.
He had heard
youpi’s words earlier
and was deeply moved by them.
( Menthuthuyoupi chuckles )
You’re out of your mind.
That’s not even close
to a fair trade.
( Knuckle gasps )
Menthuthuyoupi: My answer...
Is no.
( Knuckle gasps )
Menthuthuyoupi: But...
Get rid of this thing,
and then we can talk.
He’s the thing
you’ve been dodging around
to protect, right?
Now those would be terms
I could agree to.
( Knuckle gasping )
Morel: No. Don’t do it.
Just think.
Don’t be a fool, knuckle!
Narrator: Due to the effects
of god’s accomplice,
morel’s desperate cry
did not reach his companion,
but meleoron came to his senses
and let go.
♪
( Knuckle gasps )
Morel: Just go. Leave me here.
Meleoron: Don’t do it.
Please, knuckle,
anything but that.
Morel: Don’t worry...
About me.
Meleoron: This battle
will have been for nothing!
Morel:
All we’ve done ’til now...
Meleoron: Think about
everything you’ve done
and morel and shoot.
You’ve all risked your lives!
Narrator: If knuckle
were to stop himself,
the two of them
could still fight together,
but for that to happen,
meleoron had to stay hidden.
That was what meleoron thought
when he let go of knuckle...
Morel: Knuckle.
Meleoron: Knuckle!
( Grunts )
Narrator:
But his plan backfired.
Meleoron: How stupid.
That’s it. It’s over.
There’s no way
we can beat youpi anymore.
Morel: Why? Damn...It.
Narrator: Seeing morel
covered in blood,
images of shoot flashed
before knuckle’s eyes,
and his will crumbled.
Knuckle: There. It’s done.
A.p.r. Is deactivated.
Now the terms are even,
so leave the boss alone.
Fight me! Kill me!
You know you wanna!
Menthuthuyoupi:
Nah, screw all that.
( Knuckle gasps )
Wait a minute!
Where the hell are you going?
Menthuthuyoupi:
To the king, of course.
I thought that was obvious.
You want to come along with me?
You’d die, you dummy.
( Knuckle gasps )
Menthuthuyoupi: His ability
is teleportation, isn’t it?
Meleoron: Huh?
Menthuthuyoupi:
Then you’d better rush
the guy in sunglasses
to a doctor, quick,
or you just made
that trade for nothing.
♪
Narrator: Protecting the king
was supposed to be
his first priority.
He should have killed them all
on the spot.
( Menthuthuyoupi scoffs )
No big deal.
You can attack me all you want,
but i’ll still
shake you off easily.
Narrator: Though it was true,
he didn’t act on it.
In a way, this irritation felt
different than his usual rage.
Menthuthuyoupi: Try me anytime.
We’ll fight as equals then.
I don’t need to kill you
right now.
That’s all.
Damn it. I sound like pouf.
Narrator: During combat,
youpi had learned
how profound nen really was.
It had also awakened his
previously meager sense of self.
Once he’d learned
to compartmentalize his rage,
his rational side
could no longer
perceive the world so simply.
His perception grew.
Menthuthuyoupi:
They’re responsible for the rage
i’ve stored, so why don’t
I feel like using it on them?
I don’t understand it.
Now that I have it,
I have to use it,
but who or what
should I use it on?
Narrator: Was this maturity?
Youpi wasn’t sure.
But knuckle,
on the other hand...
Knuckle: I lost completely.
Meleoron: Knuckle!
( Knuckle gasps )
Meleoron: We gotta help him!
Knuckle: Come on, boss.
Let’s go.
Morel: I said to leave me here.
Didn’t you hear me?
So go.
You can still fight,
the two of you.
Do what you can.
He said to try him anytime,
so go...Now.
Knuckle: I can’t.
’cause i--
I can’t see him
as just something
to exterminate now.
Morel: Knuckle.
Knuckle: You heard him.
He acknowledged
how serious we were.
He wasn’t a bad guy.
( Moans )
So why would we keep doing this?
I can’t think of a reason.
Knov: The king.
( Knuckle gasps )
Mr. Knov.
Knov: The soldiers
are of no consequence.
The king can just wave his hand
and turn all of them
into evil spawn.
( Shivering )
I’ll take care of morel.
Shoot is also safe.
Do you want
to come with me, too?
Morel: Wait. Let me hit
this little brat hard.
Knov: I just got word
from the chairman’s messenger.
( Shuddering )
He was able to take the king
to the agreed-upon spot.
( All gasp )
Knov: Even if they leave now,
the royal guard
won’t make it in time,
so consider them fired.
Same goes for you guys.
( Laughs )
Where’s palm?
Knuckle: No word yet.
Knov: I see.
Well? Now what?
I hope to come back here,
but I can’t guarantee it.
You can see i’m in bad shape.
( Both moan )
Knov: Are you going,
or are you staying?
Knuckle: We’re staying.
We’ve still got
a lot of work to do.
Knov: I see.
You’re tough.
Knuckle: Let’s go.
Meleoron: To look for palm?
Knuckle: No.
We can do that later.
There’s something else
we have to do first.
♪
Youpi’s not the only
royal guard, you know.
( Singing in Japanese )