[roars]
[narrator]
Strange beasts
and monsters.
[squeaking]
Vast riches.
Hidden treasures.
Evil haunts.
Uncharted frontiers.
The mysterious unknown.
The people who are captivated by
the magic in those words...
are called...
Hunters.
[grunting]
[Kurapika]
We entered the long and difficult path,
broke down the wall,
and from there we snuck into
the short and easy one.
Even under pressure, you were able
to calmly assess our options,
and think of a way
to get around them.
And that is what makes you so special.
HIT x THE x TARGET
[narrator] One by one,
each of the 24 applicants who passed
the third phase of
the Hunter Exam exited Trick Tower,
eager for a long awaited breath
of fresh air.
Congratulations on escaping
Trick Tower, everyone.
All that remain now are
the Fourth Phase and the Final Phase.
Only two more.
The Fourth Phase will take place
right over there on Zevil Island.
Now, let's proceed.
To begin with I will need each of you
to draw lots now.
-[surprised gasping]
-Really?
Draw lots for what?
What will that decide?
[amused] Hm. Who you hunt,
and who hunts you.
In this box are exactly 24
numbered cards.
Which means,
that one of the numbered cards
will correspond with your badge.
Now, each of you will draw a card
in the order you exited the tower.
All right.
Which of you was first?
[clicking noises]
Guess that means I'm next.
After him, I'm next.
-Oh, hey, Killua.
-Huh?
He mentioned us hunting and being hunted.
Do you think that means
we're gonna be fighting each other?
Yeah, probably does.
[whistles]
Now, I don't know
what this is all about,
but I know you've got to draw it
like you mean it.
Yeah!
[Lippo]
Has everyone drawn?
Very well. Now if you would,
please go ahead and remove the sticker.
The number you see is your target.
[gasping]
[breathes uneasily]
This box has recorded the number
that each of you drew.
Each card was tallied
and then stored in memory.
So if you like,
you're free to dispose of the cards.
It makes no difference at this point.
The objective is to steal
your target's ID badge.
Oh, good.
So we don't have to kill each other, then.
The method is up to you.
Procure the badge however you see fit.
But if you kill your target,
you can take their badge easily.
Yeah, that sure sounds like
the fastest way to me.
[sounding scared]
So that's how it's gonna be?
Come on, there's nothing to be scared of.
[Lippo]
Listen carefully!
Collecting the ID badge of
your specified target
will earn you three points. Understand?
Your own badge is also worth three points.
And all the other badges
are worth one point.
In order to move on to the Final Phase,
you will have to collect six points.
So during your time there on Zevil Island,
gather enough badges to collect six points
or fail the Exam.
Only those who do will clear
the Fourth Phase of the Hunter Exam.
[Khara] I'd like to commend all of you
on your work in the Exam's Third Phase.
I'll be your guide. It's nice to meet you.
You can call me Khara.
It will take two hours for this boat
to reach its destination, Zevil Island.
All 24 applicants who've made it this far
are granted an open invitation
to participate again in next year's Exam
no matter what!
So even if you don't pass this time,
we really hope you'll try again.
Never say die, right... everybody?
[Khara]
Wow, that went over well..
It appears the battle has already begun.
You're right.
Everybody has already taken off
their badges
and tucked them away
so they won't get stolen yet.
All right, everyone.
For the next two hours,
you're all free to do whatever you like.
Thank you and I hope you all enjoy
the rest of the voyage.
[grunts]
So, uh...
hypothetically,
if you happened to be my target, I mean...
Don't expect me to show you any mercy,
okay?
Well, of course not.
If you happened to be my target
I would say the same thing to you.
Am I your target? Really?
[chuckles]
I'm speaking hypothetically.
Oh yeah, I knew that.
We're speaking hypothetically.
Hm.
You needn't worry.
You're not my target, Leorio.
Oh, I see.
Uh, oh! So you know,
you're not my target, either.
Hey.
So, uh... Who did you get?
What did you draw?
It's a secret.
[laughing]
Don't worry about it.
You're not my target, Gon.
I promise.
That's good.
Because you're not mine, either.
You want to show our numbers
at the same time?
Okay.
Ready, and!
[gasps]
[Killua Zoldyck]
Number 44 is...
[Gon Freecss]
Really?
You've got seriously bad luck.
Oh, do you think so?
So, who is number 199, anyway?
-I'm not sure, I thought maybe you knew.
-No.
If I'd have just been smarter about it,
I would have memorized
everybody's numbers.
Once he explained it,
that's when I started paying attention.
But everyone had taken off
their badges already.
Pretty lame, huh?
[uneasy breathing]
Gon.
Oh, what's up?
Are you happy or scared right now?
Which one is it?
Oh.
Kind of both,
I guess.
If I had to fight with Hisoka one-on-one,
I wouldn't stand a chance against him.
But if all I have to do
is just steal his badge,
I don't know,
I think I might actually have a real shot.
Yeah.
The way it is now,
well, at least I've got a chance.
And to be honest,
it does scare me a little bit.
But I think it's worth it.
I gotcha.
Well, let's do our best.
Don't die, okay?
Yeah, and same to you.
[Khara] Thanks for being patient,
everyone. We've arrived at Zevil Island!
Okay then.
You will be disembarking in the order
you completed the Third Phase,
from the shortest to the longest.
Ugh, not this again.
You'll go ashore one at a time,
with two minute intervals separating
each of the applicants, all right?
I guess that means
we'll be waiting here a while.
Yeah.
[Khara] You'll be on the island
exactly one week.
That means
you only have seven days
to collect your six points
and then return to this location.
First applicant,
get ready to disembark now.
Now I understand.
The first to go ashore
have the advantage.
Right. They can hide
and watch everyone's movements,
including their target's,
before they make their move.
That's two minutes.
The second person may go.
-[clicking noises]
-[Khara gulps]
The third person may go.
Yeah, all right!
The seventh person.
The eleventh person.
The fifteenth person.
The twentieth person may go.
That's two minutes.
The twenty-first person may go.
-Bye.
Okay.
I guess I'll start off
by scouting the island.
That's two minutes.
The twenty-second person may go.
Great.
-See ya.
-Good luck.
[Gon]
First, I've got to find Hisoka.
HUNTER GLOSSARY
ZEVIL ISLAND
[Gon]
How am I going to steal Hisoka's badge?
Such a good boy.
[Gon grunting]
Very nice.
I'm beginning to get excited.
[Gon, gasping for air]
[coughing]
Hmm.
[Gon] I definitely can't get his badge
in a head-to-head fight.
It's an applicant.
And there's another one behind him.
[groans]
[Gon]
He's targeting the guy in front.
[grunting]
[cries out]
[Gon]
He missed!
That was close.
A little too close, even.
Sorry, pal, but I don't go down that easy.
[begins to slur]
[groans]
What the...
You bastard.
I coated the arrow with
a fast-acting tranquilizer.
So you're not going to be able
to walk much for about a week.
Don't worry, though.
There's fresh water nearby.
So you probably won't die.
But I'll be taking this, of course.
Later.
[Gon]
Wow.
He was able to hide his presence
while he quietly stalked his prey.
And his target sensed the shot being fired
and was able to dodge it,
avoiding what would've been
a serious injury.
But, the stalker had that covered,
coating his arrow with poison.
So that's how you hunt!
If I'm going to have any chance
of stealing Hisoka's badge,
that's the only way.
First, I'll have to sneak up on him
without being noticed,
then wait for my chance,
and take it!
[yelling]
All right!
But this target's not moving
like Hisoka will be.
[sighs]
Either way,
I'll only get one shot.
I've got to hook his badge
while he's not paying attention,
or I don't stand a chance.
[grunts]
Okay.
Try to read his movements.
[yelling] And now!
[grunts]
[Gon] Aw.
This won't do it.
It's way too easy
to follow a swinging target.
I already know exactly where
it's gonna go.
[croaking]
That's right.
I've got to remember,
he'll try to move out of the way.
[water running]
[Gon] If I can't catch a flying bird
by watching how it moves,
then I'll never be able to steal
Hisoka's badge.
[grunts]
Almost.
Oh well.
I really can't expect to catch a bird
on my very first try.
[yelling] There!
All right! [grunts]
[sighs]
Got to figure out
whose number this is.
The sun is just about to set.
I should probably stay in one location
until morning.
[panting]
Damn. I didn't think
all this was going to be so hard.
It's way too dark for me
to see anything.
And there aren't any birds out
anymore.
Guess I'll start fresh in the morning.
All right, now it's back to training!
[Gon grunts]
[panting]
It's hopeless.
Maybe this is impossible.
Catching a bird mid-flight...
accurately?
What was I even thinking?
Hm?
But, if a bird can catch a fish
while it's swimming...
There it goes!
That's it!
That's the key.
That's how I can tell
when my target's going to move.
Now!
[grunts]
I did it!
I figured it out!
I've just got to go for the target
the moment it goes for its prey.
[man]
Huh, the kid's impressive.
He actually mastered
the art of the hunt.
But concentration like that
will come back to bite you. [snickers]
[narrator] Gon finally mastered the trick
that would aide him
in his hunt for Hisoka.
However,
unbeknownst to him,
Gon was being hunted himself.
[Gon] Next time.
"Explosion x of x Deception."
-Explode!
-[Killua Zoldyck] Explode!
[Gon] Kaboom!
[Killua] Oh, mushroom.
Subtitle translation by
Mitsuko Kitajima