Gon: Kite is still alive.
( Killua gasps )
Gon: He would never be beaten,
not by something like that.
So now we get strong,
and we find him.
We’re gonna go save kite.
♪
( Singing in Japanese )
Narrator: Gon and killua
have vowed to save kite,
but before
they can return to the ngl,
they must fulfill
the one condition set
by chairman netero, the leader
of the extermination team.
Gon: What are those, killua?
Killua: They’re shogi tiles.
You take a piece of marked wood
and split it.
Then you give each half
to a different person.
You can use it
as proof of identity
or to verify a document.
Netero: We have already
placed two assassins
in the nearest city.
Killua: In this case,
each of the two assassins
have the other halves.
We’ll beat ’em
and take their pieces.
( Overlapping chatter )
It’s been erased.
That means someone
checked the board.
( Gon grunts )
♪
Woman: You must be
killua and gon.
It’s nice to meet you.
My name...
Is palm.
It’s a pleasure.
Ah, don’t be like that.
There’s no reason to be nervous.
I imagine the chairman didn’t
tell you very much, did he?
Allow me to explain.
Let’s sit down
and have some tea.
( Boys grunt )
Palm: I am knov’s pupil,
you see.
He told me I would
only get in his way,
but I insisted
on accompanying him.
Gon: Who’s that?
Killua: Don’t know.
One of the guys
with chairman netero?
Palm: Yes,
the one in a black suit.
My teacher is a wonderful man,
cool and intelligent
and composed.
Oh! Cool and composed
mean the same thing.
I only admire him. That’s all.
There’s nothing romantic
or anything.
Except i’m not certain
of that either.
( Nervous laugh )
I mean, respect is
a considerable factor
when it comes
to falling in love, after all.
( Gasps ) And my teacher knows
nothing about this, of course.
I have never said a word
to him, and I never will.
( Slurping )
( Boys groaning )
( Palm sighs )
Though in matters of the heart,
you can never
really say for certain.
Love is a spontaneous thing.
That goes without saying.
Don’t you agree?
Killua: Uh, can I interrupt?
Aren’t we supposed to fight you?
Palm: Huh? Oh, dear, yes.
I apologize.
The chairman and my teacher
said I couldn’t accompany them,
which is quite unfortunate,
if you ask me.
But I insisted on going
with them. I had to.
It feels like I spent a lifetime
trying to prove
my determination to them,
but they finally conceded,
with a stipulation.
- ( Laughs )
- Killua: Not what I asked.
Palm: I know
what you’re thinking.
My teacher seems so cold,
but he’s actually kind.
That’s easier to see
once you’ve spent
as much time with him as I have.
Ah! Of course,
by "spending time with him,"
I don’t mean that he and I are--
killua: Agh!
What is the condition?!
Palm: You have to take down
knuckle and shoot.
It’s unthinkable, really.
How dare those vulgar,
rude, barbaric brats
go to the ngl before me?
I simply cannot allow it.
Gon: Whoa!
Hey, miss palm, please,
you’ve gotta stop
using your hatsu!
( Wiping )
So she’s an enhancer like me.
I don’t like this.
Killua: Hold on.
"Knuckle and shoot"?
So you’re not here to fight us?
- Palm: That’s right.
- ( Both gasp )
Palm: After all, I am not
the one who’s been assigned
to defeating knuckle and shoot.
That job belongs to you.
( Both grunt )
Palm: You see, knuckle and shoot
are students of Mr. Morel.
♪
They, too, received a condition.
Unfortunately,
I don’t know what it was,
but I know this.
Whether it’s us or them,
only one group will be allowed.
We only have one month’s time.
Hunter: Okay. We were told
to keep these tiles
in our possession for a month,
so you can bet
that in that time
someone’s gonna come for them.
So, knuckle, what do we do?
Knuckle: Strike first,
and we win.
We’ll find ’em, and...
We’ll kill ’em!
♪
( Amplified )
My name is knuckle bine,
and i’m a beast hunter!
Extermination team candidates,
I challenge you to a duel!
Midnight tonight,
and don’t be late!
Fight me fair and square!
I won’t try to hide or run away!
I won’t bring weapons or allies!
It’ll just be me and me alone!
So come and fight me, okay?!
Man: Where?
Man #2: What location?
Man #3: You have to to tell them
where to find you.
Knuckle: Bring it on! Hear me?!
A man knows never
to turn his back on an enemy!
I’m prepared to follow you
to the ends of the earth!
You won’t get away from me!
Killua: I wouldn’t go,
even if he said where.
He’s just a decoy.
His partner’s
probably hiding somewhere.
You know,
i’m even willing to bet
that they’re watching to see
if anyone reacts suspiciously
before they make a move,
and according to palm,
they don’t even know our names,
- so we’re in the clear.
- Gon: Mm-hmm.
Killua: They were just trying
to lure us out somehow.
Only an idiot
would pull a stunt like that.
Gon: What did the guy look like?
Was he powerful?
Killua: He’s tough.
Gon: What’s it gonna take
to defeat him?
Killua: Your guess
is as good as mine.
One of the hunters
with the chairman
said that in a battle
nothing is certain.
Also according to that guy,
i’m not qualified to judge
if a fight can be won.
But I disagree.
If you want to survive,
you have to increase
your odds of victory.
Gauging
the strength differential
between you
and your opponent is key.
( Slurps )
If you’re fighting someone
you could only beat
once or twice out of
a hundred tries, don’t bother.
( Gon gasps )
Killua: You want
50-50 at least...
70% or better
if it’s at all possible.
And for us
to get to that point,
there are still two things
we have to do.
We need to work
on all our fundamental skills
and learn about
our opponents’ abilities.
( Gon grunts )
Killua: If we find out
what they are,
we can plan ahead just like
we did against genthru.
Gon: Hmm.
Half of me agrees with you,
and half doesn’t.
Killua: What does that mean?
Gon: I agree that we should
work on our fundamentals.
I just don’t agree
we need to know
exactly what
their abilities are.
Killua: Really?
Why the hell not?
Come on!
Why add to all the risks
without any real benefits?
Gon: I know,
but once we’re inside,
that is what we’re
going to be facing.
( Killua gasps )
Gon: Our goal isn’t
to defeat knuckle and shoot.
It’s to get stronger,
strong enough to go back
to the ngl and rescue kite.
♪
I mean, we’ve gotta be powerful
enough to beat enemies
we don’t know anything about
at a moment’s notice.
If we always need to plan ahead,
then what’s the point?
Killua: That’s true,
but we’ve still gotta beat
these guys first.
After all, we only have a month
to get this done, remember?
Gon: That’s too long.
Killua: Eh?
Gon: Seven days.
In one week, we’ll get
strong enough to go back!
Killua: Ah? Bu--
- ( gon yelps )
- Bisky: Are you an idiot?!
( Killua gasps )
Gon: Huh?!
Boys: Biscuit!
Bisky: Mm-hmm.
Boys: Why are you here?
Palm: Because I
invited her to come.
Boys: You two know each other?
Palm: No. I just did
a little research on you.
Gon: Okay, but we
only know her from--
- ( palm laughs )
- ( Boys gasp )
Palm: Once I used my ability,
it was really quite simple.
There’s no time left to spare,
so let’s begin.
We must plot to kill
Mr. Morel’s disciples.
Boys: No, thanks.
Bisky: Now let’s get started.
Boys: Osu!
( Gon gasps ) Ohh!
That hurt! What was that for?
Bisky: I’m picking up
where I left off.
What are you, an idiot?
That old man is notorious
for being very unreasonable.
( Netero laughs )
Bisky: If he tells you
to do something in only a month,
then it will probably
take you at least a full year,
and that’s if you’re lucky.
There’s no way you’ll
defeat them in just a week.
Gon: But you don’t understand!
We have to get back there
as soon as possible
so we can save kite!
Bisky: Wait.
What are you talking about?
♪
Neferpitou:
That was so much fun.
It felt like a dream.
I’d love to do it again...
With you.
Bisky: I see.
Well, that’s all the more reason
you can’t rush your training.
( Gon groans )
Bisky: What if you make
those same mistakes again?
Killua: At her age,
no wonder she’s a pro
at chewing people out.
Bisky: Do you understand?
Gon: Osu.
Bisky: Let’s start
your training, then.
Show me ren.
♪
All right, now. You are to
maintain that for three hours.
( Both gasp )
Gon: Killua,
how long can you go?
Killua: On a really good day,
I can do
just about 55 minutes Max.
Bisky: Do that, and then we can
move on to the next step.
Train like your lives
depend on it.
( Laughs )
( Gon panting )
( Killua groans )
Bisky: Oh, come on.
You didn’t even last an hour.
Okay, now keep going!
They say it should take
about a month
to prolong your ren
by a mere ten minutes.
That means we can’t spare
any time for sleep.
( Dog whimpers )
Knuckle: Damn them.
Those damn bastards
didn’t even show up!
You cowards deserve to die!
( Dog barking )
( Groans )
Okay, you’ve got a collar,
so where the hell’s your owner?
You gotta pick up
after your dogs.
Keep our parks clean, damn it.
Bisky: All right!
That’s enough for today.
Tomorrow begins in 30 minutes.
( Boys snoring )
Bisky: And from the looks of it,
now would be the perfect time
to use my ability.
Hmm.
♪
Well, you’re up, cookie. Go on!
( Piano playing )
Magical spa services
peachy relief--piano massage!
( Gon sighs )
( Bisky sighs )
- Palm: Excuse me.
- Bisky: Huh?
Palm: I do hope
i’m not rude for saying this,
but i’ll let you choose
how to train them.
My ability selected you
as the answer I seek, after all.
However, if after a month,
we determine
it would be impossible for them
to defeat morel’s pupils,
I sincerely doubt that I would
be able to restrain myself.
I must go to the ngl.
I want to go right now, in fact.
If i’m forced to wait
and wait and wait and wait
and then I don’t get to go...
Then i--i may end up
killing you all.
Bisky: Wait. Was that a threat?
Palm: No, just a warning.
I don’t want to hurt you.
Therefore if you don’t think
they stand a chance,
you should give up sooner
rather than later.
My anger won’t be
as terrible then,
judging by my past experiences.
Bisky: I’m really not the one
you should be telling that to.
You can tell the two of them
when they’re awake, okay?
Gon: You don’t have to worry.
We’ve got this.
We’ll get you inside the ngl,
no matter what it takes.
So if you have any pointers
for me or anything like that,
you can let me know, okay?
I’ll try hard!
( Grunts )
( Palm gasps )
Bisky: That’s how he is.
Just have faith in him.
( Gon grunting )
( Palm sighs )
( Heart beats )
- Oh, dear! Oh, gosh! Oh, no!
- Bisky: Hmm?
Anyway, at the moment,
i’m far more concerned
about the guys back in the ngl.
What exactly does the chairman
plan to do for the next month?
Hey!
Palm: Uh, oh,
they said they were
going to "scout and whittle,"
try to identify and chip away
the enemy strong points.
The experts
can’t come to a consensus
on how much time remains
between now and
when the king is born.
The chairman is acting
on the assumption
that the earliest it will be
is in two months.
Netero: Hmm.
This isn’t good.
That thing looks
a lot stronger than me.
Knov: Stronger than you,
chairman?
Surely you jest,
’cause if that’s the case,
not a single hunter
in the entire world
will stand a chance against it.
( Netero chuckles )
It’s been more
than half a century
since I was the strongest
among nen users,
but I do see your point.
And although i’m flattered,
i’m currently just about even
with the two of you.
Knov: Then you’re more
than strong enough, chairman.
You should be more confident.
Netero: Even when i’m at less
than half my former glory?
The ravages of time
come for us all.
Knov: Always ready
with a comeback.
Morel: But we’ve
still gotta fight ’em.
Netero: I would prefer
to avoid that eventuality.
A nonviolent solution
would be a much better outcome.
Our target is the queen
and the queen alone,
but it will be quite difficult
to slip through
his en surveillance.
There’s no way
to avoid confrontation.
The only question
is how we’ll manage to win.
If you have any ideas,
i’d be glad to hear them.
Knov: You love to tease,
don’t you?
You already knew
what you would do
when you chose the two of us,
didn’t you?
♪
We go and exterminate the ants
silently one at a time.
( Morel inhales )
Now let’s take it slow,
all right?
Might as well enjoy the job
while we’re at it.
Okay. To start with,
let’s find exactly out how many
opponents we’re up against.
Now go.
Neferpitou: Hmm?
Hmm.
So many. Something is coming...
But they’re not alive.
Is this the enemy’s ability?
What to do meow?
Male: You might as well wait.
Neferpitou: Hmm?
Male: Because I can assure you
that if they get this far,
we will simply destroy them.
Neferpitou: I guess
you have a point there.
It’s possible
that they’re decoys.
Hey, wait a sec.
Was I just speaking out loud?
Male: Oh, no.
I simply happened to know
what you were thinking about.
Neferpitou: And who
are you, anyway?
♪
Male: I am one
of the queen’s royal guards.
Call me shaiapouf.
( Chuckles )
( Heart beating )
Menthuthuyoupi
will soon awaken as well.
Neferpitou: Meow I get it.
So you’re shaiapouf.
Shaiapouf: Well,
a mere observation.
Neferpitou: So you can read
my thoughts, can’t you?
I’m not sure I like it.
Shaiapouf: I can understand
the sentiment.
( Chuckles )
Neferpitou: But soon--
( giggles ) He’ll awaken.
That’s wonderful news.
’cause, you see,
I still haven’t
made a final decision
about exactly what ability
I should develop.
Oh, yeah! It’s so simple!
All I need to do is fix him.
That’s what i’m
gonna make my ability.
Then i’ll be able
to once again experience
that dreamlike moment with you.
( Laughing )
( Boys groan )
( Panting )
Bisky: Come on!
What are you doing?
At this rate, you’re never going
to defeat knuckle and shoot,
much less the chimera ants!
Are you giving up
on going to the ngl?
( Gon groaning )
No way.
We’ll never give up!
We will go back to the ngl!
I don’t care what we have to do!
( Both yelling )
( Palm gasps )
Gon: We’re going back
to save kite.
( Palm groans )
Narrator: After reuniting
with biscuit,
gon and killua
are back to training.
They have but one goal, to get
strong enough to rescue kite.
That motivation is pushing gon
to his absolute limits.
♪
( Singing in Japanese )