Killua: Nanika’s really good
at breaking,
but when it comes to fixing,
not so much.
When she heals, she has
to touch the target directly,
or her power won’t work.
I’ll save gon and alluka, too!
♪
( Singing in Japanese )
♪ You can smile again
( singing in Japanese )
♪ You can fly away
( Traffic rushing softly )
( Monitor beeping steadily )
( Ventilator hissing )
( Footsteps approaching )
( Woman gasps )
♪
No, I can’t.
There’s no way
I can remove this.
My power isn’t strong enough.
This burden,
it’s insurmountable.
( Morel scoffs )
Killua! Where are you?
You okay?
Killua: Yeah.
I’m on my way back.
How’d it go with gon?
Morel: No luck.
When we told him all about kite,
there was no response
on the monitors.
A lot of people
have already come by
to visit and talk to him, but...
No reaction so far.
Killua: I understand.
I doubt he can be healed
by conventional means.
Morel: Hold on.
Calm down, killua.
It’s like you said before.
Gon used a contract
with conditions
to get an immense amount of nen,
but it was only temporary.
Isn’t that right?
In that case, it’s best
if we let a nen exorcist
take care of it.
At this stage in the game,
it’s way too late
to be taking any risks.
Killua: Oh, sorry.
I guess I phrased that wrong,
so let me clear it up for you.
Thing is, i’m not talking about
some crazy gamble or anything.
In fact, I can guarantee
gon will be healed.
Let me take care of this.
My way isn’t nearly as risky
as using a nen exorcist.
Morel: Hmm.
Killua: Right now, our only
real problem is getting there.
That’ll be
our biggest challenge.
Let’s focus on doing that.
Morel: Wait. What do y--
- ( click )
- ( Killua gasps )
Gotoh: Forgive me,
master killua.
Killua: Gotoh?
Gotoh: On the grounds
of secrecy,
I can’t allow you
to continue that call.
Killua: But I didn’t
tell him anything!
Gotoh: Not true.
You said you could guarantee
gon would be healed.
That was a reference
to master alluka’s power.
At the moment, you are still
barely within zoldyck property,
but outside the boundaries.
Your outing precaution level
is already at four,
so watch what you say.
Killua: I get it now.
He was just waiting
for me to give morel a hint.
You’re way too soft.
You know that?
Gotoh: I’m afraid I don’t
understand what you mean.
Killua: Level four. Wow.
Looks like
I really pissed off dad.
Narrator: Outing precaution
level four,
when in this classification,
the subject’s words and actions
are restricted,
and they must be supervised
by multiple butlers
and family members.
Any violation,
no matter how small,
will result in the subject’s
immediate capture.
They are then sent home
and upgraded to level five.
Level five, the target is
not allowed to leave the estate.
Any attempt at escape
will be put to a swift halt.
Killua: Fill me in.
Gotoh: These precautionary
measures are recommended
due to removal
of family valuables,
as well as rebellion and
hostility toward your parents.
Killua: She isn’t property!
Gotoh: There are
three prohibited matters.
The first, outsider contact
is strictly forbidden.
This includes speaking
or passing objects
without the express permission
of the family.
To enforce this,
the target is forbidden
to carry
any communication devices.
Killua: Yeah,
you took everything already.
Gotoh: The second,
you must remain
within a one-meter radius
of master alluka.
There are absolutely
no exceptions at any time.
Killua: Fine. I don’t plan
on letting her
out of my sight anyway.
Gotoh: Thirdly,
to protect family secrets,
master alluka’s ability
must be kept confidential.
Sharing minor details
is forbidden.
( Killua sighs )
Yeah, I get it. Basically...
This is how
it’s gonna have to be.
This way,
I don’t have to ask permission
for every little thing.
Not only that,
but now you can take care
of all our travel arrangements.
Gotoh: That’s all well and good,
but may I ask you
what canary is doing here?
Killua: Idiot! Alluka’s a girl.
Do you really think
a stupid dude like you
can take care
of all of her needs?
Woman: I wouldn’t
worry about that.
( Killua gasps )
♪
Woman: We’re happy to accompany
you as well, killua, dear.
Master silva believes that
you two might not be enough,
so he sent us along
in order to help ease his mind.
Killua: Tsubone!
Dad’s even more pissed
than I thought.
It’s fine.
I won’t do anything stupid
at level four.
Tsubone: Listen to me,
killua, dear.
If you think i’m as lenient
as your father and gotoh,
you are sorely mistaken.
A single violation,
big or small,
and you will be sent back home.
Resist,
and I will knock you out.
I would keep that in mind
if I were you, so are we clear?
Killua: Uh, yes, ma’am!
Gotoh: Tsubone sensei
is the only person
in the entire household
who can call young master killua
"killua, dear."
Alluka: Don’t bully
my big brother, okay?
Tsubone: I’m so sorry.
Alluka dear is so kind,
aren’t you, sweetie?
Won’t happen again.
Killua: I just realized
I have a lot of trouble
dealing with old ladies.
Tsubone: You love
your big brother?
( Alluka giggles )
A whole bunch!
Tsubone: That’s nice. And are
you going to do as he says?
Alluka: I sure will!
Canary: Master killua is
depending on me to assist him,
all so he can save his friend
with no regard for the risks.
I must help him.
I don’t care
if it costs me this job
or even if it costs me my life.
( Canary sighs )
Amane: Amane. Nice to meet you.
Canary: I’m canary,
and likewise.
Alluka: Tsubone...
Give me your fingernail,
the pinky one.
♪
Killua: She made
a demand of tsubone.
The timing couldn’t be worse.
Even I don’t know when nanika’s
going to make demands
or who she’ll make them to.
Tsubone: Of course.
It would be my pleasure.
( Crunch )
Master killua,
I believe i’ll go into hiding
for the time being.
At least, this way,
young master alluka
won’t be able
to demand anything further
from anyone else.
Everything will be on me.
Have I made myself
perfectly clear?
Of course, I will never be
far away from the two of you.
Alluka: Aww.
I had more things I wanted.
♪
Killua: Damn it.
It’s all right.
I still have the advantage.
I won’t be able to make a wish,
but I can still give an order.
( Gasps )
Alluka: Hey, big brother,
you mad at me?
Killua: Mm-mmm.
It’s okay.
There’s nothing for you
to worry about, alluka.
I’m gonna save them.
I swear it.
( Cell phone rings )
Gotoh: Yes?
That’s right.
Correct.
That’s correct.
This is
master killua’s cell phone.
Killua: Mm?
Gotoh: No,
I can’t answer that question.
I can’t answer that one,
either.
I suppose, in that case,
perhaps it would behoove you
to state your name first.
Good afternoon.
Killua: Who was it?
Gotoh: It was just--
- ( cell phone rings )
- Hmm?
( Beep )
Hello.
( Leorio inhales )
Let me introduce myself!
My name is leorio!
Do you think that I
could maybe speak to killua?!
Would that be possible?!
Morel: Shh!
Killua: Wow, that takes me back.
Gotoh: It has been
quite some time, master leorio.
Leorio: Huh?
Oh, yeah, I remember!
You’re the coin guy!
Gotoh: Master killua’s
on his way,
and he will be accompanied
by us, of course.
That’s right,
to help master gon.
However, there are going
to be a few conditions.
Leorio: Wait. What?!
Conditions to save a friend?
Are you dreaming or something?
I’ll be glad to talk louder
if that’s what it takes
to wake you up!
Gotoh: Shut the hell up, peon.
Leorio: The hell did you say?!
Gotoh: Master killua’s
risking his life.
- ( Leorio gasps )
- Gotoh: He’s heading to you
against the wishes
of his family,
and I don’t think
I have to remind you
how special
the zoldyck family is.
See, we’re the ones
who make requests.
Now shut up, and listen, punk.
Killua: Gotoh.
Gotoh: You’re right.
Sorry for the outburst.
Killua: I’ll talk.
It’s faster that way.
- ( Gotoh grunts )
- Don’t worry.
I won’t say anything
i’m not supposed to.
Wouldn’t wanna
get sent home, would I?
Hey. Been a while.
Leorio: Killua!
As soon as you get here,
i’m totally gonna kill
that guy! Are you okay?
Killua: Yeah, but I
can’t say anything specific.
Trust me, okay?
Do whatever gotoh says.
( Leorio groans )
Fine. Whatever.
Just put the guy back on.
Morel: I’ll ask
about the conditions.
Let me talk.
Leorio: You’re, uh,
morel, aren’t you?
It’s my phone.
I’m talking to my friend,
so can you give me
one good reason
I should end our conversation
so you could start your own?
Morel: That’s a good question.
The answer is
just hand over the damn phone.
Leorio: Not gonna happen.
Now get lost.
Morel: Very well.
I’m only trying to help you out.
You’re probably gonna say,
"sorry, but it just
can’t be done. Impossible."
And then you
should hand over the phone.
Know why?
’cause i’m the guy
who can get it done.
♪
Leorio: You still there?
No. No, it’s nothing.
Tell me the conditions.
Gotoh: When we arrive,
there mustn’t be anyone else
inside the building.
Except for master gon himself,
there is to be no one else
on the premises.
Leorio: No doctors?
Gotoh: None.
Leorio: No other patients?
- Gotoh: Correct.
- ( Leorio sputters )
It can’t be done!
That’s impossible!
This is a public hospital!
Do you have any idea
how many thousands of people
are in here?
( Leorio growling )
Morel: Hello?
I know what the conditions are.
Yes, i’ll take care of it.
Gotoh: How, exactly?
Morel: It’s a big hospital,
and it’s got a big parking lot.
We’ll set up a private wing
for gon there.
I’ll make it so you can
drive in and out of the area.
You’re gonna want to be
away from prying eyes.
Nobody will know
what you’re doing in there.
Gotoh: Understood.
That satisfies our requirements.
And you are?
Morel: Name’s morel.
Gotoh: In the future, you will
be the one that I speak with.
Morel: There you go.
( Leorio growls )
Morel: Oh,
gotta make another call.
( Line ringing )
Hey, knov. It’s me.
There’s been
a slight change in plans.
I need for you
to make sure the equipment
can be fully controlled
from outside.
No, can’t have monitors.
And no windows.
That’s true.
They don’t want to be seen,
so it sounds like
they have a nen exorcist,
but killua made it sound
like it’s something else.
♪
The association’s exorcist
made it sound
like gon was beyond help,
but killua said
he’d be healed with no risks.
( No audible dialogue )
Not yet.
I don’t think we should ask
any more questions.
Killua said
we should trust him.
There aren’t too many rules
on the battlefield,
but when a trusted ally
says something like that,
you shut up and listen.
Leorio: Mr. Morel,
i’ll leave all contact
with killua up to you.
Morel: Thanks.
I won’t let you down.
What are you gonna do?
Leorio: I need
to find some people,
because i’ve got a thing or two
I need to say to them.
♪
( Phone line ringing )
Gon’s fighting for his life.
Where are you,
and what are you doing?
Pick up the phone...
Kurapika.
( Cell phone buzzing )
( Buzzing stops )
Pariston: And so
we zodiacs are unanimous
in our utmost respect for
the previous chairman’s wishes.
We promise to honor his memory
as we take great strides forward
for the association.
So it doesn’t make a difference
who you vote for,
and, no matter who gets
your support, your vote counts!
I say that
with absolute certainty!
I’m sure there are those of you
who are dissatisfied
with the current association
or who would like nothing more
than to see
a brand-new administration.
However, there are much better
ways to express those feelings
than choosing to abstain
from this critical vote!
We’re here so that you
can ask questions
or address the crowd yourselves!
The point is to make
your voice heard, so speak up!
Even if your opinions
aren’t popular ones,
you will not be ignored!
In fact, ging here
is a prime example.
He’s committed more violations
than I can count,
and yet look where he’s sitting.
He’s still here among us,
a proud member of the zodiacs!
If you’re thinking
about abstaining,
why not vote for him instead?
That was a joke, of course.
This election
is the very last mission
that the former chairman
decided to give to us,
and I believe
that the association
should work together
in order to complete it!
( Applause )
Piyon: Okay.
Thank you very much
for your speech,
vice-chairman.
You can return to your seat
and sit down now.
Make it snappy.
We’ll now open the floor
to everyone here.
If you’d like
to express your views
or simply ask a question,
let us know
by raising your hand.
Yes, you there.
The tall guy in the dark suit.
Go ahead.
♪
Leorio: I’m leorio,
exam term 2-8-7.
I’ve got a question for ging
that I want answered.
That’s him, gon’s dad.
Why haven’t you gone
to visit gon yet?
You’ve got to know what
condition he’s in. Don’t you?
( Hunters murmuring )
Piyon: Right.
Let’s all settle down
so we can hear the answer.
Ging: To begin with,
who are you to gon?
Leorio: His friend.
Ging: Oh. I appreciate that.
I hope you’ll stay friends
with him. That’s all, so...
Leorio: You didn’t
answer my question!
Just visit him!
Go before it’s too late,
damn it!
Ging: Well, from all
the stories i’ve heard,
he has quite a few friends
like you,
and what i’m saying
is that that’s enough.
Leorio: This is
not the time to mess around!
Don’t you care?!
Do you even have any idea
how much gon’s
wanted to see you?!
If you would
just go and talk to him,
who knows? Maybe that
might help him start to recover!
Ging: Did he say
he wanted me to come?
Did he tell you that?
He said those words?
( Leorio sputtering )
Like he’s in any condition to.
♪
Bastard.
( Roars )
( Hunters murmuring )
( Ging swallows )
Leorio: Die, you asshole!
- ( Hunters cheering )
- Piyon: Wow!
I don’t think
anyone saw that coming!
And if you want to see it again,
you’ll find footage of today’s
meeting on the hunter website,
so tell everyone
who wasn’t here,
and let ’em know they can
watch it whenever they want!
♪
As a matter of fact,
make them watch it!
( Singing in Japanese )