Killua: Been a while
since I flipped my switch on.
( Neck cracks )
♪
Gon: Scissors!
Rammot: Hey, there, Colt.
Check this out.
It almost feels
like i’ve been reborn!
♪
( Singing in Japanese )
( Fly buzzing )
Narrator: The hunter association
has learned of the chimera ants
from the biological survey team.
They are now awaiting
the world leaders’ decision
on how to handle them.
♪
Politician:
We’re counting on you.
You have only one mission
to carry out,
the immediate execution of all
of these dangerous creatures.
Netero: There have
already been many casualties.
We will proceed
using any means necessary.
Will that be acceptable to you?
Politician:
Well, yes, of course.
We wouldn’t dream of telling
the experts how to proceed.
All we desire now
is for those dangerous creatures
to be eradicated as swiftly
and humanely as possible.
Netero: Yes, of course.
I understand.
So their goal is
to eradicate the ants,
leaving the hunter association
to take the blame
for the fallout.
I get it.
( Keyboard clacking )
Lin: Th-the hierarchy
inside of a chimera ant colony
has f-five total ranks,
with the queen at the very top.
♪
( Both grunt )
Stick: There’s the queen.
Right under her
is the royal guard
and then the squadron leaders.
Spin: And directly underneath
them are all the officers.
They oversee the foot soldiers
as well as the other grunts.
Lin: T-that’s correct.
A-and after the king is born,
th-the hierarchy will shift
just like this.
Banana: The royal guard
that followed the queen
would switch and
enter the king’s service.
Lin: And a-afterwards,
all the squadron leaders
will report
directly to the queen,
and she would then
shift her focus
to directing the soldiers.
Stick: The queen
remains in the castle,
periodically
giving birth to more kings.
Banana: Then the kings travel
and mate
with different organisms,
all for the purpose
of breeding new queens.
( Spin groans )
No wonder they spread so fast.
Banana: The only way
to prevent proliferation
is to kill the queen before
she can give birth to a king,
but first there are
the soldiers.
All of the ones that guard her
will have to be defeated.
Stick: That’s a tall order.
( Cell phone buzzing )
Spin: Mm-hmm.
Mm.
All right. We’ll be waiting.
The first extermination team
is coming.
Stick: "Extermination"?
Banana: I wonder
who they’re sending.
Stick: Yeah, considering
they’ll be facing
those vicious chimera ants.
They must be strong.
Banana: They’d better be.
I’m worried about kite
and the kids.
Spin: They’ll arrive
in three days.
( Wind blowing )
( Nen whooshes )
( Rammot laughing )
( Colt gasps ) How?
Rammot: Look at this! Ha ha!
Isn’t it just incredible?
Colt: Why does he have
so much life energy?
There must have been
some sort of trigger.
A trigger.
♪
( Gon yells )
Jan Ken...
Rock!
( Rammot gags )
( Groans ) It hurts!
Colt: I wonder. What if
their attacks were the catalyst?
( Rammot roars )
I can feel the power filling me!
Colt: Peggy...
Peggy: Uh-huh.
Colt: Remember when I said
we’re capable
of anything humans are?
Peggy: Including
this bizarre power?
But--but this is...
Colt: Rammot, hit me
while you have that power.
Peggy: Wait.
Colt, what are you doing?
♪
Rammot: You’ve really
been pissing me off lately,
so I won’t hold back.
Colt: It may need to be
quite hard to take effect.
( Rammot sighs )
Fine. Then I guess
I don’t have to go easy on you.
Colt: Bring it.
( Rammot yells )
( Colt gulps )
( Peggy gasps )
Colt!
♪
Hagya: This is
a message from hagya.
This is a message from hagya.
Some prime prey is hiding
in or around the factory.
Capture them.
Capture them...
Dead or alive.
Capture them!
Flutter: Lord hagya.
Hagya: What is it?
Flutter: Do you believe
that they will succeed?
Hagya: I believe that
an entire group of officers
should put up
a pretty good fight.
Flutter:
"Pretty good fight," huh?
I hope so.
Hina: I’d like to agree,
but I really doubt
they’re gonna be much help.
Hagya: I’m fine with that.
Hina: You are? Why’s that?
Hagya: Because they’ll
buy a little time
until we can get there.
Hina: Oh. I see.
Flutter:
Well, if that’s the case,
then the rares
will be ours for the taking.
( Hagya sighs ) Exactly.
♪
( Wolf ant pants )
( Boys gasp )
Kite: We’re surrounded.
And by a lot of ’em, too.
♪
( Whoosh )
( Gon gasps )
( Grunts )
( Whoosh )
Frog ant: All right, then.
Shall we decide how we kill you
and in what order?
You guys have three choices.
I would pick wisely
if I were you.
One, choose the order
you want to fight.
Two, you can try to escape.
Three, surrender
and let us capture you.
Pick the first option,
you will be able to fight us
one-on-one in direct combat.
You may even survive.
I don’t recommend
the second option.
If that is the choice you make,
you will only anger us,
and you will suffer far more
as a result.
Option three is the worst choice
you could make.
That is the one
that would anger us
even more than option two.
( Chimera ant laughs )
Frog ant: Now then,
what will you do?
Gon: Kite.
Kite: We couldn’t have asked
for a better deal.
( Boys grunt )
Kite: One-on-one
with their officers.
Whoever is ready for a fight
will go first.
Killua: I’ll go.
Gon: No, I will!
( Boys grunt )
Show me rock!
Rock-paper-scissors!
( Killua groans )
Gon: Okay. I’m going first.
Kite: They’re exhibiting
human personality quirks
at the expense of their
characteristic ant teamwork.
I only hope that we’ll be able
to take full advantage of that.
Dog ant: Okay, let’s figure out
which of us goes first.
( Can rattles )
Number six.
It’s six! Who has it?
( Armadillo ant laughs )
Lucky me.
Frog ant: Baro, is it?
Gon: How do we know it’s over?
Baro: Huh?
It’s obvious, isn’t it?
Whoever dies loses.
Gon: Wait.
So we can’t surrender?
Baro: What?!
( Chimera ants gasping )
Baro: Are you crazy, kid?
If you lose, then we’re just
gonna feed you to the queen.
There’s only one way you’re
getting out of this alive,
and that’s if you defeat me.
Gon: Fine. I can agree to that,
but you don’t have to die
if you’re the one
who ends up losing this.
If I win, i’m not gonna eat you.
( Baro growling )
Gon: If you surrender,
i’ll let you live.
But if you lose,
you have to promise me
that you’ll never eat
another human being,
not for as long as you’re alive.
( Boar ant laughs )
I don’t think he knows
who he’s dealing with.
Wolf ant #2:
He’s got a lot more spunk
than any prey i’ve ever seen.
Chimera ant #2:
Yeah, lucky you, baro!
Baro: You’re dead!
♪
Damn it! You dodged that one.
All right, fine!
Then how about this?!
Killua: The same attack?
( Gon gags )
Killua: Gon!
Kite: He changed direction.
Gon: I’m okay.
( Baro laughs )
How the hell are you so tough?
Come on! Every one
of the other humans
puked their guts out.
Whatever. I could
keep this up all day long,
but you’ll never be able
to dodge my homing attacks.
♪
Kite: He’s right.
He only has to change his course
to match the direction
gon dodges.
Well, gon, what will you do?
Baro: Listen up.
There’s something you
should know before you die.
The main reason
that we kill humans
isn’t so we can
eat them ourselves
or even so we can
feed them to the queen.
Gon: So why do it?
Baro: Because it’s fun,
of course!
( Gon grunts )
Baro: I love the sound it makes
when you humans
puke out your guts with a plop.
( Imitates gagging, laughs )
It almost sounds like
a bad case of the runs!
Gon: That isn’t funny at all.
( Baro yells )
I’m gonna make you vomit
your own organs
with a plop, too!
( Gon yells )
( Grunting )
( Yelling )
( Baro gasps )
Wolf ant #2: He didn’t dodge.
Boar ant: Yeah, he stopped him.
( Baro grunting )
Gon: Compared to razor’s spikes,
this is actually
a piece of cake!
( Crash )
( Shell cracks )
( Chimera ants murmuring )
Killua: All right.
We’re kind of in a hurry, so...
♪
Who’s my opponent?
Frog ant: Who’s next?
( Can rattling )
Dog ant: Number three.
Number three’s up!
Rhino ant: Settle down.
You’re too cocky
for your own good.
I’m about to show you
what hell looks like.
Got that? Don’t lump me in
with trash like him.
- Gon: Trash?
- Rhino ant: Yeah.
I call ’em like I see ’em.
Got a problem with that?
( Gon grunts )
Rhino ant: Come on.
I’m at least ten times
stronger than that guy.
Killua: Okay. So not much, then.
Rhino ant:
What did you just say?
Kite: When they
enter combat mode,
their aura becomes
much stronger than usual.
They’re suited for this.
Gon’s slow start
does make me a bit anxious...
But we can still make it.
We’ll reach the queen before
she can give birth to the king.
But why?
I have a bad feeling.
It’s like i’m missing something.
♪
There’s a gnawing anxiety
that won’t go away.
Rammot: Check this out, Peggy!
( Chuckles )
I can control it now.
This energy is mine to command!
This is incredible!
( Laughs )
Peggy: We should conduct
more research.
Rammot: Hang on. What?
Peggy: If we learn
the proper way
to wield this power, then
perhaps we can synchronize it
with our own abilities and make
an even stronger weapon.
Rammot: Heh.
You’re such a stiff...
- ( Slap )
- You know that? Gimme a break.
Colt: Zazan...
( Gasping )
A few days ago, she told me
that she had captured a rare.
If we’re lucky, he might
still be in the storeroom.
Find it, and secure it.
♪
( Rhino ant laughs )
Sorry, but my entire body
is covered with hardened skin.
Keep it up. I can take as many
of those attacks as you’ve got.
Killua: Oh, really?
( Rhino ant groaning )
( Gags )
( Chimera ants murmur )
Killua: Is there anyone here
ten times stronger
than this guy?
Kite: What a pleasant surprise.
Their officers
can be dispatched easily.
Maybe i’m worrying over nothing.
Let’s find out.
Frog ant: That’s enough.
It’s my turn!
( Crazy slots babbles )
Two!
( Frog ant gasps )
♪
Kite: Two, huh? Not a good spin.
Gon: Hey, killua.
Killua: Mm.
That scythe, it’s bad news.
Kite: Gon, killua,
in three seconds, jump.
( Both gasp )
Frog ant: W-what is this?
Why do I feel so scared?
Yes, that’s right!
I think i’ve experienced
this sensation before!
I remember now.
This is death.
This is what it’s like
to be dominated
by a superior creature.
( Queen bites )
( Gon gasps )
Kite: Disappear.
Unfortunately,
this is the only technique
I can use with the scythe,
and it won’t disappear
until i’ve used it.
( Sighs )
It’s so annoying.
Killua: Yeah, so why did
you make it that way?
♪
Kite: Be careful as we advance.
Like I told you before, they’re
still alive for a little while.
You okay?
Because it’s only going
to get worse from here on.
If you’re thinking
about the enemy,
you won’t be able
to last mentally.
Gon: I’m all right.
I don’t have any sympathy
for guys like him
who call each other trash.
Kite: That’s the problem.
Would you act differently
if one of those bugs
cared for its friends?
Narrator: Kite, gon, and killua
head toward
the chimera ant queen’s fortress
with one singular mission
on their minds,
preventing the birth
of the king.
( Hagya grunts )
♪
( Singing in Japanese )