♪
( Guns cocking )
( Man laughs )
♪
What? Intruders?
Get rid of them.
I’m far too busy at the moment,
so don’t bother me
with pointless reports!
( Hangs up )
( Dishes clatter )
Please, continue.
♪
( Singing in Japanese )
King: Hmm?
officer: I don’t know
which nation’s army sent you,
but by virtue
of setting foot in here,
you’ve earned a painful demise.
Neferpitou: Your highness.
King: Mm.
I don’t even find the need
to strain my eyes
to see its presence.
It’s a rare...
And it’s piquing my appetite.
( Slashing )
( Chuckles )
That’s it, the flavor I seek.
Yes! I can feel it.
This is it!
( Neferpitou gasps )
( King laughs )
It’s surging through my body!
Neferpitou: Meow I get it.
This is the king’s power.
By consuming the aura of
the rares, he makes it his own.
In other words,
the more he eats,
the stronger he grows.
( Leader clapping )
( Muffled laughter )
( Door bangs open )
Hey! Who are you? Guards!
What do you think you’re doing?!
King: He’s worthless.
I don’t sense anything at all.
Leader: Insolent thugs!
Have you any idea who I am?!
i am the absolute leader
of this era, a king among kings!
I am masador Diego!
King: Someone tell me
why this scum
is claiming to be a king.
Shaiapouf: It seems to me
that in the human world,
it’s a very common phenomenon.
Humans without intelligence
or talent
end up in positions of power
due to heredity or connections.
King: That defies all logic.
In the hands of an incompetent,
power brings nothing but ruin.
this must be
the work of imbeciles.
We must keep humans
on a very short leash.
Neferpitou: Sire.
They can provide you
with quality meat, however,
not to mention the fact
they are a fully
self-renewing resource,
quite easy to harvest.
Even the commons can be used
as an acceptable food source
for soldiers like us.
( Diego growls )
You’ll leave here at once
if you know what’s good for you!
Or taste my divine pow--
- ( body thuds )
- ( Glasses clatter )
( Women whimpering )
neferpitou: Please,
allow me to take care of this.
he can be used
to control the humans.
King: Do as you like.
Woman: Wait! No!
Please, spare our lives!
we beg of you!
( King laughs )
these humans
are complete idiots.
Now I want you to think
as hard as those puny brains
of yours can manage.
have you ever
spared a pig or a cow
because it begged you
for its life?
Yes.
The view is excellent,
and there’s plenty of space.
We’ll call this place
the meat orchard,
and we’ll use it
as a human processing plant.
Neferpitou: Sire.
♪
Narrator: After losing
to knuckle and shoot,
gon and killua return
to the inn where palm waits.
Killua: Before I worry
about enemies,
I have to protect gon from palm.
( Creaking )
( Killua gasps )
( Palm gasping )
You’ll pay for this.
( Both gasping )
Palm: You promised me.
You swore that you
would take me to the ngl.
you said
if you broke that promise,
you would stick a thousand
needles in your eye.
( Gon grunts ) I’m sorry.
Palm: I have no interest
in an apology.
There’s no point in having you
stick needles
in your eye, either.
( Gon grunts ) Is there
a way that I can make amends?
Palm: Let’s see.
There is.
you must accomplish any
one task that I set before you.
killua: Wait a sec!
Think about how gon is feeling.
Gon: Fine. Okay.
Palm: Go out with me.
( Both gasp )
Palm: You must...
Go out with me.
( Killua gasps )
Gon: All right.
Killua: Huh?
Whoa, are you crazy?!
Do you have any idea
what you’re doing?
Gon: Mm-hmm, but I promised.
I said i’d do anything.
Killua: Is this really
how you want it to happen?
Just think for a second!
Palm: This is none
of your business.
It’s between gon and me,
and it’s settled.
Just between gon and me.
Oh, goodness. Mmm!
( Giggling )
( Killua shudders )
I’m telling you, man,
you need to stay away from her.
Palm: And you need
to stop interfering!
This is between
gon and me, remember?!
killua: You just want
an excuse to keep saying that!
Palm: Oh, shut up!
Gon and I are going on a date,
and that’s final.
Besides, there’s somewhere
I really want to go.
Gon: Oh, sorry. Not today.
( Palm gasps )
Gon: I have to train
with killua today, but...
I know! Why don’t you
come train with us, palm?
( Palm gasps )
What are you talking about?
We are going out.
You promised me, didn’t you?
Gon: Mm-hmm.
Palm: Then why
is he tagging along?!
And why would we train, anyway?!
You must be joking!
We’re dating, and this
will be our first date!
You hear me?!
Our very first date!
Our first date.
( Panting )
Gon: But it’s
not actually a date.
( Palm gasps )
Gon: See, we can have
a real date later on.
Since it’ll be our first date,
we should do it right.
Killua: Wow. I’ve never heard
the word "date" so much.
Gon: And I really want
to be prepared,
so i’m gonna need
some time to get ready.
Palm: Prepared? For what?
Gon: Secret! I won’t tell.
just wait,
and you’ll find out tomorrow.
Palm: Oh.
Well, in that case, all right.
Sorry.
If you would have
explained that first,
I wouldn’t have gotten so angry.
Gon: No, it was my fault.
I just wanted to surprise you,
thought it might be fun.
Palm: Oh, my goodness!
A surprise for me?
I’m keeping an eye on you.
( Giggles )
( Killua shudders )
gon: All right.
Then let’s meet in front
of the bulletin board
at 10 A.M. tomorrow.
Palm: I’ll be there.
killua: Wow,
you’re amazing, gon.
Gon: What do you mean?
killua: It’s just
when I heard you talk to palm,
it seemed like you were
right there in your element.
Gon: Really?
( Killua sighs )
there’s something
I wanted to ask you about.
Gon: Hmm?
Killua: Have you ever
been on a date before?
Gon: Sure, plenty of times,
except most all of them
were with my aunt mito.
Killua: Oh. Okay, I get it now.
Wait. So does that mean
that there were others?
Gon: Yep. Sometimes ships
with all-female crews
would stop by whale island,
and some of them
would only go out
with guys who were
younger than them.
I’d show them around town,
and they’d teach me
a bunch of stuff.
Killua: "Stuff"?
Hold on. That means...
He’s so experienced.
( Gon chuckles ) They call
women like that cougars.
Isn’t that crazy?
Haven’t you ever been
on a date, killua?
Killua: Huh? No way!
I was too busy. All of my time
went to assassin training,
and we’ve been together
since I retired.
Gon: Oh, yeah.
Killua: You get it now?
and I thought
we would stay together.
Bisky: One day, you will
leave gon behind to die.
( Echoing )
...Die. ...Die.
Killua: Damn. I’m losing it.
I’ve already made up my mind.
( Cellphone ringing )
Gon: Yeah? Hello.
Knuckle: It’s knuckle.
We’ve located and secured kite.
gon: Really?
So kite is okay, then?
You still there?
Knuckle: I have
reason to believe
that kite is being
controlled by the enemy,
so i’d like to tell you
he’s okay, but I can’t.
Gon: Don’t worry.
I’m sure there’s some way
we can bring him back!
Knuckle: All right.
It’ll take three days
for us to reach your location.
In the meantime,
be on the lookout
for any soldier ants.
They’re scattered all over,
imitating the king.
Gon: Right.
( Stifled yell )
All right!
I knew that kite
was still alive!
Killua: That’s great.
All I have to do now
is protect you for a month.
Piece of cake.
( Cheetu humming a tune )
( People gasping )
Woman: Oh, wow!
Woman #2: Look over here!
( Cheetu stops humming )
( Laughs )
( Thinking )
I’ve found new feeding grounds.
( Slurps )
( Water flowing )
Gon: Found it!
Killua: Okay, but what’s it for?
gon: This?
It’s a present for palm.
Killua: Are you sure about this?
don’t you think
she’ll go totally berserk
if you just hand that to her?
gon: Hmm.
Well, by itself, probably.
Killua: Anyway,
let’s go back to town
and see what’s happening there.
Gon: ’kay.
♪
Killua: If we run into
any soldier ants
here in the mountains,
we’ll be in serious trouble.
On the other hand,
if we stay in town,
we’ll probably encounter
ants looking for humans,
but we can try to escape
while other people
are being targeted.
after all,
gon can’t use nen right now,
so i’ve gotta protect him,
even if it means sacrificing
everything else.
- ( Brush rustles )
- ( Gasps )
( Animal bleats )
Killua: Let’s hurry up.
( Sirens blaring )
( Tires screeching )
Detective: Drop your weapon!
Place your hands
behind your head,
and get down on the ground!
We’ll give you until the count
of three before we open fire.
One...
- ( Cheetu yawns )
- Detective: Two...
Three!
Cheetu: Ready.
Detective: And fire!
♪
Officer: He disappeared.
Aah! ( Screams )
( Officers screaming )
Cheetu: You’d think
they’d be faster.
This is no fun.
Newscaster: And in other news,
at around noon today,
an unidentified creature
killed seven people
in the suburbs of pata.
it injured
multiple police officers
that rushed to the scene
before escaping
into the miera mountains.
According to the authorities,
the creature moved faster
than 200 kilometers per hour.
It then said it would return
and that they should
bring someone faster,
which suggests it could be
a new species of magical beast.
A mandatory evacuation order
is in effect...
Killua: Pata city
and the miera mountains.
Another city’s between us,
with the miera mountains
on the opposite side.
We should be okay.
Newscaster: The government has
submitted a capture request
with the hunter association.
The association has accepted.
- And now the weather.
- Gon: Hey, killua!
- All done!
- Killua: Right.
( Turns off TV )
Gon: I guess tomorrow
we’ll both be on our own, huh?
killua: Yeah.
I’ll be training at the gym
pretty much the whole day.
Yeah, right.
I can’t just leave gon alone
when he’s vulnerable.
Palm: Gon, over here.
Gon: Huh?
♪
Hmm?
( Palm giggles )
Gon: Huh?
( Gasps )
I didn’t even recognize you!
Killua: Who are you?!
Palm: Do I look strange to you?
gon: Mm-mmm.
You look really pretty!
Palm: Oh, no, please stop it.
You’re being far too loud.
It’s just so embarrassing.
gon: Huh?
I’m just telling the truth.
( Palm giggles )
That’s enough.
Come on. Let’s go.
( Killua groans )
♪
Damn it!
What the hell am I doing here?
it’s like i’m
the creepy stalker or something.
No. I can’t let it get to me.
I have to protect gon.
there’s no telling
when the enemy might show up.
How far are they gonna go?
♪
( Gasps ) It’s here.
It’s probably aura
from a soldier ant.
It isn’t that close, but it’s
not that far away, either.
There are faint traces
of aura here.
Did it already pass through,
or was it carried over
by the wind?
either way,
i’ll probably run into it.
Should I warn them?
Gon: Well, this is it.
Palm: What?
Ah.
♪
It’s so pretty!
Killua: No.
If I told them now,
it wouldn’t help anyway.
Besides, gon can’t use
his nen right now.
If he gets all upset about kite
and flies off the handle,
then he’s done for.
And knowing palm,
she’ll go 100% nuts
if I interrupt her date.
If she breaks the silence
with her screaming,
any ants that are nearby
will notice us for sure.
Palm: Thanks, but i’m fine.
( Giggles )
( Gon chuckles )
Killua: I can’t let them know.
( No audible dialogue )
I’ll handle this myself.
♪
( Gasps )
rammot: Ah.
I thought I smelled a human.
( Killua gasps )
It’s him.
Rammot: I remember you.
That’s right.
You’re one of those brats
from before.
It looks like your luck’s
run out, kid.
You’re about to get
a taste of hell
you’re never gonna forget.
of course,
it won’t last forever, you know.
Killua: I’ve led him upwind
far from the two of them.
At least I could do that.
Still...
rammot: So where’s
that little friend of yours?
Once you tell me his location,
i promise you
that i’ll make it quick.
Well, he can’t be that far.
He is your friend, isn’t he?
It doesn’t matter
if you talk or not,
i suppose.
I’ll just walk around
making lots of noise
and swinging your severed head,
and it won’t be long
before he comes to find me.
That’s how humans are.
am I right?
Killua: He’s right.
I beat him right here and now,
or it’s all over!
I’ve gotta protect gon,
no matter what it takes.
♪
( Singing in Japanese )