Bisky: My name’s
biscuit krueger,
and i’m a professional hunter,
but i’m not too big
on formalities,
so you guys
can just call me bisky.
In return, you must obey
every word of what I teach you
without question.
Killua: Ugh. No way,
and, no, thank you.
He and I are not so desperate
that we need to beg
a total stranger to train us,
so you could
just forget about it.
Am I right, gon? Back me up!
Gon: Uh, thing is,
Mr. Wing is already training us.
Killua: Yeah, that’s right!
We already have a master.
Position’s filled,
and we are not in the market
for another one.
Bisky: Did you say wing?
That little boy
with the messy hair and glasses?
The one who never
tucks his shirt in?
Gon: You know him?
Bisky: Well,
of course I know him!
Wing is one of my students,
or he was.
Killua: Really?
Gon: Wow!
What a coincidence, huh?
Bisky: So wing’s
become a master now, has he?
Time really does fly,
doesn’t it?
Does that mean both of you are
professional hunters as well?
Gon: Yeah. Well, just me.
Bisky: And you passed
the secret exam, too?
Gon: Yep.
Bisky: Wow,
that really takes me back.
I’d love to be
an examiner again.
Well, I guess that would mean
that I am essentially
your master’s master.
Now that that’s out of the way,
let’s start training!
♪
( Singing in Japanese )
Gon: That is so awesome!
You were really
one of the examiners
for the hunter exam?
Killua: Well, i’m not convinced
that she’s telling the truth.
Bisky: You sure are a stubborn
little boy, aren’t you?
That’s a good thing.
In kids, anyway.
Now, you mentioned before that
you weren’t desperate, right?
Book.
Gon: What’s that card?
Bisky: Notice that the
difficulty to obtain is rank d.
It’s a normal card
that doesn’t go in
a specified slot in your book.
There are a lot of people
who could have obtained
this card without much trouble.
The same
can’t be said for you two,
and that’s the problem.
If you run into someone
who’s stronger than you are
or someone whose intentions
are completely evil--
( gasps ) Quick, sit down.
Pretend we’re just chatting.
There’s an enemy behind me.
♪
Man: Three kids’ll
be a walk in the park.
( Giggles )
I’ll tear them to shreds.
Bisky: Don’t try to sense him.
He’ll notice.
Killua: Then how
did you sense him?
Bisky: He let
his bloodlust leak out.
It wasn’t much,
and it was just for a second,
’cause he’s
not threatened by children.
Killua: He must be weak,
since he lost control.
Bisky: But then he
concealed his presence again
almost immediately.
The bloodlust was minimal,
and his reaction was swift,
so he’s very experienced.
Killua: We couldn’t even
sense his presence,
let alone locate him.
What should we do now?
Bisky: Wow,
he adjusts pretty quickly.
He’s a bright one.
What do you think we should do?
Gon: Well, we should
definitely stick together.
Bisky: And why’s that?
Gon: I think the reason
he tensed up again
is because there are
three of us right here,
so if we stick together,
he might think twice
before attacking us.
Killua: Yeah, I agree.
Bisky: I guess
I can’t argue with that.
But that’s
not what we’re going to do.
You see, if I go off on my own,
the enemy is almost guaranteed
to target me,
so i’ll go south,
and you head north.
Walk about 500 meters
without trying
to conceal your presence.
Aim for that pillar.
Once you get there, use zetsu.
Then get back here immediately.
Killua: Right.
Stalking the stalker, huh?
Gon: Huh?
Bisky: Be that way,
you big dummy!
Killua: That damn hag.
Bisky: I’ve had
just about enough!
I’m leaving!
Killua: Yeah, well, get lost,
and don’t come back, okay?!
Come on. Let’s go.
( Gon gasps ) It’s an act.
Killua: So long, you idiot!
( Man giggles )
( Wind blowing )
Killua: That woman
is pretty amazing.
Gon: Huh?
Killua: I was on high alert
so i’d be ready for anything.
Even so, I didn’t realize
what she’d done
until my cheek
was already stinging.
Now let’s hurry back.
Gon: Yeah.
( Scissors snipping )
( Man laughing )
♪
I cut it! I just cut your hair.
You see, that...
Was my scissor hands:
Barber slasher!
And now i’m gonna eat it.
When I consume the hair I cut,
I learn things about its owners
that they don’t even
know about themselves.
I absorb everything!
Muscle tone,
potential for disease,
genetic strengths,
i’ll learn everything
there is about your body
before I start
to toy with it, everything!
( Gasps )
Wait! She’s 57 years old?!
She doesn’t look it.
What’s even more surprising
is how honed her body is.
I can tell.
Her physical appearance
conceals the strength
that she’s achieved
through intensive training,
decades of it, probably.
If I may ask,
i’d like to spar with you.
Bisky: So I guess you’re
not just trash after all.
Fine. Let’s go.
( Yells )
( Man groans )
♪
Bisky: You’re really lucky.
In a nen battle,
I would have annihilated you.
So during that fight,
what did you see first?
Gon: The first thing I saw
was that guy being flipped
through the air.
Killua: Me, too.
Gon: Her opponent
wasn’t weak at all.
Killua: She’s just
that powerful.
Bisky: If he were
an in-game character,
he’d be difficulty rank d,
in other words, an instant
game-over for you boys.
And I believe
that makes this the second time
i’ve seen you escape death
by the skin of your teeth.
How long do you think
your luck’ll hold out?
Gon: So, hey, miss bisky--
bisky:
Please just call me bisky.
But if you insist on honorifics,
call me lady bisky!
Killua: I think i’m
just gonna stick with "hag."
( Screams )
Gon: Okay, bisky,
why are you here?
Bisky: I came here
to clear the game,
but also there’s
a Jewel i’m looking for.
Gon: A Jewel?
Bisky: And it’s one that can
only be found around here.
It’s specified slot number 81.
It’s called blue planet.
What about you boys?
Killua: I thought it was obvious
that we’re here
to clear the game.
Gon: Yeah, but also
my dad and his friends
- actually made "greed island."
- Bisky: Really?
Gon: I’m looking for him,
and I don’t know where to start,
but this game
just might contain a clue
about where I can find him.
Bisky: And who is your dad?
Gon: His name’s ging freecss.
- Bisky: Seriously?!
- Gon: You know him?
Bisky: Yes,
of course I know him!
Ging is famous!
♪
Chairman netero used to say
he’s among the top five
nen users in the entire world.
Gon: Bisky, if you’d be willing
to postpone your treasure hunt,
we’d be honored
if you’d teach us nen.
Bisky: So you
finally came around.
You should know in advance
that i’m no softie like wing.
Are you ready?
Gon: Yes, I am!
Bisky: And you?
Killua: I’ll be all right.
( Man coughing )
Bisky: Now hurry
and take out your cards.
Man: Book.
Bisky: You get one chance.
Evade these two successfully and
for two weeks, you understand?
And if you do,
then i’ll let you go.
However, if you’re
knocked unconscious
or if you can’t
stand up anymore,
i’ll just have to kill you.
( Both grunt )
Man: So I just have to avoid
their attacks, right?
Doesn’t matter what I do to ’em?
Bisky: That’s right.
But there’s one rule.
Under no circumstances are you
allowed to leave this crater.
If you break this rule,
you lose, and I kill you.
Killua: What about us?
Bisky: The same rule applies.
If you leave or if you
can’t beat him after two weeks,
you will be punished.
You are the bounty hunter
binolt, aren’t you?
Binolt: Yeah.
Bisky: He’s also
a bounty himself.
He’s a brutal murderer.
( Binolt chuckles )
Bisky: Now begin!
♪
( Binolt exhales )
Bisky: What are
you waiting for?!
Are you going to stand there
while he heals his wounds?!
Killua: If he
wasn’t hurt so bad,
I would have lost my eye.
( Binolt coughs )
Gon: I can’t find an opening.
Killua: I wonder
if I should try using this,
but it’s not like he’s gonna
stay still while I charge up.
Let’s make this
a battle of attrition.
Gon: What’s "attrition" mean?
Killua: You go
and get a little rest.
I’ll stay and keep an eye on him
for now and use these to attack.
Switch every six hours.
Gon: He’s using rocks?
Good idea!
( Binolt chuckles )
Just what I need.
If I can rest like this
for a week,
i’ll be pretty much recovered,
and as soon as i’m healed,
I can finish them off.
Bisky: Huh.
♪
( Binolt gasps ) A shield?!
Bisky: That’s right!
You’ll never defeat him
in an endurance test!
Killua: That makes sense.
Binolt: Damn.
( Crashing )
( Panting )
So much endurance.
I don’t have any time to rest!
Bisky: Binolt is hurt,
but overwhelming him in
half a day is still impressive.
They know that in this fight,
their lives are on the line.
Not bad.
These two are gems in the rough!
Look at that hard resolve
in his eyes,
that bottomless,
unwavering potential!
If properly cut
through training,
he can be completely transformed
into a true diamond.
And this one’s
a cool, calm blue.
He looks unstable, but apply
the right amount of heat,
and he can achieve
permanent strength,
a true sapphire.
( Sighs )
Why does my heart skip a beat
whenever I see something
waiting to be polished?
I’m gonna train them so hard!
A forest of rocks.
It impedes the enemy
while concealing their presence.
This isn’t gonna take two weeks.
They’ll be done in a day.
Looks like it’s game over
for you, old man.
No! Killua, stop!
( Binolt grunts )
Killua: Why didn’t you
let me finish him off?
Gon: We still have
plenty of time.
Let’s keep going until we
can deal with him one-on-one.
Killua: Huh?
Gon: Stopping now
would be a waste of time.
We’re both pretty much
in top form right now.
( Binolt laughs )
You idiot.
It’s my turn.
I’ll cut you to pieces!
Gon: Okay, but let’s
wait ’til tomorrow.
Binolt: Huh?
Gon: It’s just I can tell
you’re getting a lot slower,
so you should probably go
and get a little rest.
Killua: Hmm, he’s right.
If it takes both of us
to beat somebody
who’s badly injured
and completely exhausted,
we’ll never be able
to beat anybody.
( Animal howls )
( Both grunt )
( Binolt groans )
Bisky: You won’t
be able to slip away,
not now that their antennae
are so perfectly tuned.
Sorry, binolt,
but your potential pales
in comparison to theirs.
- ( Crowd murmuring )
- ( Baby crying )
Woman: My wallet’s missing.
Man: Really? It was just there.
Boy: ’scuse me.
Both: Huh?
Boy: You, uh, dropped this.
( Gasps )
( Gasping )
Bisky: All right, day two.
♪
( Both grunting )
Killua: He’s slowing down.
No, we’re getting faster.
The difference is amazing.
Training pays off that much more
when you’re fighting
for your life
against one of your equals.
( Yells )
Bisky: Damn it.
♪
Damn it!
( Gon yells )
Binolt: No.
This isn’t the life I wanted.
I never asked for this!
( Objects clatter )
Woman: I warned you, didn’t I?
Man: You were the one
who suggested
that we take a shortcut!
Woman: So it’s my fault?
Man: Just look at my clothes!
They’re covered in filth!
Binolt: It’s not like I was
asking for a reward or anything.
I didn’t even expect
a thank-you.
I just...
( Killua grunts )
Binolt: Enough already.
There’s no way I can beat you.
Just kill me.
Gon: But why would we
want to do that?
We’ve gotten a whole lot better,
and it’s all
thanks to your help,
so thank you, Mr. Binolt.
Binolt: All I wanted...
Was to live
as a decent human being.
Bisky: You may go.
Binolt: I’ll go turn myself in.
Bisky: Gon...
You certainly are
a flawless specimen,
but that purity of yours
is going to make this
quite the balancing act.
Okay! It’s time
we head to masadora!
Both: Osu!
( Both gasp )
The number nine!
Bisky: Too slow!
Now give me 3,000 push-ups!
Both: Damn it!
Bisky: 70 kilometers to go
in, oh, say, three hours?
Should be a breeze.
Both: Seriously?!
♪
Gon: Hey, we’re here!
Bisky: Come on!
Help me
look for a department store!
Gon: Just like we thought,
they’re only selling cards here.
Bisky: Sorry for the wait.
Now let’s head
back to that rocky area.
Both: What?!
( Panting )
Bisky: Gain!
Gon: Wait. These are the cards
you bought
at the department store?
Bisky: Sure are.
Okay, let’s head back
to masadora now,
but this time,
we go in a straight line!
Killua: Wait.
A straight line, huh?
You don’t mean--
bisky: I do!
It’s time to start digging!
Killua: Not as hard
as I was expecting.
Gon: Yeah, it should go pretty
smoothly if this keeps up.
♪
( Both groan )
Killua: This is rough.
Gon: I can’t do any more.
Bisky: What are you doing?
Sit up if you’re gonna rest.
- ( Killua groans )
- Gon: Huh?
Bisky: Starting today,
this is how you sleep.
Don’t let go of the rope.
There’s always
a chance I might cut it,
so keep part of your brain
on high alert,
even when you’re sleeping.
Killua: My dad
used to put me through
this kind of training
all the time.
Gon: Ow! That really hurt!
Bisky: One more thing,
when it falls,
you have to put it back up.
( Digging )
Killua: Oh, man, your head.
Gon: I feel fine.
Bisky: I’ll be
making the rocks bigger.
Killua: Hey, gon--
gon: I said i’m fine.
( Yells )
This rock is a lot harder
than the rest of it.
Killua: Maybe we can dig it up.
Gon: Hmm. I don’t think
the shovel’s gonna work.
But I think it might be possible
for me to bust it open
with a nen punch. ( Gasps )
Killua: What’s wrong?
Gon: Killua, what are you
doing with your aura
when you’re digging?
Killua: Nothing that’s
out of the ordinary, I guess.
Try thinking of the shovel
as an extension of your body.
( Killua gasps )
I see.
If we envelop
the shovel in aura,
our digging will be enhanced.
Gon: Wow! It’s like
the rock’s made of custard!
Killua: Okay!
Then let’s keep digging!
Bisky: It sounds
like they’ve learned
a new application of ten, shu!
They’ll complete the first phase
by the time we reach masadora.
♪
Narrator: Bisky’s grueling
training process is under way,
but how it will affect the boys
remains to be seen.
( Singing in Japanese )