Narrator: Chairman netero
gathered the top leaders
of the hunter association,
a group known as the zodiacs,
for the purpose of electing
the next chairman.
The zodiacs are composed
of 12 hunters
whose abilities
the chairman recognized.
He trusted them to lead
the association in emergencies
and expected them to spar
with him in his free time.
Each member
was given a code name,
and most of the zodiacs,
out of loyalty to the chairman,
adopted their new name
legally and officially
and altered their appearances
to match the theme,
though there were exceptions.
♪
( Singing in Japanese )
♪ You can smile again
( singing in Japanese )
♪ You can fly away
♪ You can fly!
( Singing in Japanese )
Man: Chairman!
( Sobbing )
Mizaistom: I thought all
of the zodiacs were called up,
but the rat’s missing.
Piyon: Even at a difficult time
like this,
the vice-chairman
is incredibly busy.
Geru: Now more
than ever, really.
I’m sure he’s scrambling
to secure votes.
( Ginta sobs )
Why, oh, why did you have
to leave us, chairman?!
Cluck: Ginta, calm down!
Shut up! You stink!
Saiyu: Even that chronic no-show
ging’s here.
I guess the rat just sucks.
Ging: "Even ging is here"?
You’re dead, monkey.
Saiyu: I’d like
to see you try, dumb-ass.
Botobai: I can’t accept this.
Why didn’t the chairman
call us to help?
It doesn’t make any sense!
Kanzai: We’re stronger!
Well, for all
intensive purposes.
Cheadle: You mean
"intents and purposes."
You wanted to hunt them
yourself. That correct?
( Botobai groans )
Saccho: We’ll decide
all together,
like the chairman said.
I say we wait.
Pariston: Really sorry
i’m late, guys.
It won’t happen again.
Everyone is in a real frenzy
over east gorteau.
Gotta admit i’m wiped out.
( Laughs )
Mizaistom:
Just sit down already.
Pariston: Oh. Pardon me.
Let’s start this meeting
by discussing elections
for the next chairman.
Kanzai: Wait a minute!
I don’t remember
giving you permission
to run the meeting!
Pariston: Is that
a problem for you?
Piyon: You show up late,
and then you
start bossing us around?
Cluck: Pariston, leave!
You creep! So annoying!
Pariston: Yeah, I guess
that was a bit forward.
You’ll have to forgive me.
But the fact remains
that I am the vice chairman.
Not only do I outrank you,
but i’m an excellent mediator,
and we all want
to wrap this up quickly.
That’s all I was thinking.
Mister botobai is
the most senior,
and miss cheadle is best
at fostering progress.
Both are better suited
to the task than I am.
You want to lead?
We can switch.
Cheadle: I’ll refrain.
I would just get derailed.
( Pariston chuckles )
Botobai: Same here.
Saiyu: Forget it.
Just start the meeting.
We can all tell
that you want to, you creep.
Pariston: Well, in that case,
how many of you are opposed
to me moderating this meeting?
A show of hands should suffice.
Cluck: I object!
I object! I object!
Pariston:
That’s four objections,
but the majority rules,
so I will continue.
If you’re not satisfied
with my performance,
please let me know.
I’m happy to withdraw
at any time.
Now, then, I do have a proposal.
I nominate myself as chairman.
We’ll skip the election.
Ginta: Do you wanna die, brat?
Well, do ya?
Pariston: Hey, calm down.
You guys are scaring me.
Skipping the election would save
a lot of time and money,
and we all know
i’m the right choice.
Geru: Not a single one of us
would ever cast a vote for you.
- Pariston: That’s 11 votes.
- ( Geru groans )
Pariston: All together,
you only total 11 votes.
Know how many hunters
there are in the association?
The late chairman netero
was far too strong.
That’s why
he couldn’t relate to the weak.
The same can be said
for you guys,
while I, on the other hand,
can empathize.
That’s the kind of chairman
i’ll be!
Piyon: Then explain
why the weaker hunters
are all slaves
to your temp agency.
Exactly how much money
have you made off of them,
o prince of kickbacks?
Pariston: That was
a big misunderstanding.
My account was used,
but it was only held
as a reserve fund
to back the association.
Mizaistom: Pariston,
does the number 18
ring any bells for you?
In the three years since
you became the vice-chairman,
that is the number of hunters
who’ve gone missing.
We’re pros who risk our lives.
We’re obligated to keep track
of our colleagues
out in the field.
A hunter dying is one thing.
A missing hunter
is something else.
Before you became vice-chairman,
the average
was .6 hunters missing a year.
It’s increased tenfold.
Care to respond?
Pariston: That is unfortunate.
It breaks my heart,
but once I am chairman,
- i’m sure it’ll go down.
- ( Mizaistom grunts )
- Ging: I nominate myself.
- Both: Hmm?
Ging: I’ll follow
the old man’s wishes.
♪
Zodiac: I don’t want to vote
for either of them!
Pariston: Mister ging, isn’t
your son having some trouble?
Ging: Sounds like it.
Pariston: Would you like me
to pay him a visit?
Ging: Sure.
I bet he’d love that.
Pariston: What? ( Laughs )
That seems unlikely.
I heard he’s still
in critical condition.
I guess maybe I shouldn’t go.
He could be dead
by the time I got there, right?
Ging: Nah, go.
That kid’s not gonna die.
Pariston: I’d like
to say something.
I feel like we should
probably reconsider
these self-nominations.
- Mizaistom: Hmm?
- Kanzai: But you’re the one
who started it, dumb-ass!
What in the hell
is wrong with you, huh?!
Pariston:
I just offered to serve
as a way of saving
valuable time and money.
Since we’re bound by procedure,
we should decide
on the process first.
( Kanzai growls ) Here we go.
Mizaistom: We’ve let him
run things before,
and everything
always gets complicated.
Cheadle: In that case,
let’s draw lots.
Saiyu: Huh? Hey, screw that!
A raffle?
That’s no way to pick a leader.
You a scumbag, too?
Cheadle: We’ll each
get a sheet of paper.
Saiyu: Hey, wait!
Cheadle: I want
each of you to write down
what you believe is
the optimal election process,
and I ask that you bear in mind
that our ultimate goal
is a 95% quorum.
Then all we have to do
is let a third party
pick a proposal at random.
Botobai: A third party?
Geru: Beans.
Who else could she mean, right?
Cheadle: Each one
has a 1-in-12 chance.
That way,
there are no hard feelings.
( Kanzai groans ) I guess so.
Saccho: Yeah, good idea.
Pariston: I concur,
since i’ll win anyway.
But I propose
that we write down our names
so that we know
whose idea is chosen.
♪
Saccho: She said the odds are
1 in 12, but that isn’t true.
If all ten of us
write down something
that puts pariston
and ging at a disadvantage,
if that’s even possible,
our odds will actually
be five in six. Not bad.
Cheadle: If the voting is
anything less than anonymous,
that will
definitely favor pariston.
What if we make it anonymous
and nominate
multiple candidates?
Those indebted to him
can betray him
with little fear of reprisal.
Well, there you have it,
Mr. Beans.
Inside of here, there are
12 folded sheets of paper.
You need only draw one.
It will determine the rules
we will use for the election.
Beans: Me? You’re sure?
That’s a lot of responsibility.
All right. Here goes.
And the winner is mister ging.
♪
( Saiyu scoffs )
Ging’s rules.
Mizaistom: He’s no pariston,
but he’s still trouble
in a different way.
Beans: "Rule number one:
All hunters
"will be both nominated
and be eligible to vote.
"Rule number two:
If the winner of the first vote
"fails to get a clear majority,
"there will be a revote
with the top 16 nominees.
"If further revotes are deemed
necessary by the same criteria,
"the pool must be culled
in half before proceeding.
"Rule number three: If voter
turnout is less than 95%,
"only that vote
will need to be repeated.
"Rule number four:
"Votes need to be signed
by the hunters casting them.
Anonymous votes don’t count."
Kanzai: What in the hell
were you thinking?!
Cluck: Making people sign?!
Public votes?!
Are you a complete idiot?!
Ging: You guys are the idiots.
I mean we have to know
who voted for whom,
because it’s
more fun that way.
Kanzai: That’s his problem.
The only thing
he cares about is having fun.
Beans: "Rule number five..."
Both: How many are there?!
Beans: "Chief executive officer
of the election task force
will be Mr. Ging freecss."
Mizaistom: That clever bastard.
Cheadle: I should have
thought of that, but I didn’t.
Saccho: I was too focused
on the actual rules.
Botobai: So that’s
his true objective.
Now he can manipulate
the election
all he wants
without interference.
Pariston: May I say something?
This was to determine
the voting process, was it not?
I love rules one through four,
but the executive
should be chosen separately.
Ging: Fine.
Just one through four, then.
Zodiac: You’re okay with that?
Beans: That’s a real hunter.
How frightening.
( Door opens )
Mister ging! Hello!
Ging: Hey.
Beans: What brings
you here so early? Heh.
I’m a little surprised
you actually came.
Ging: Oh. Yeah, I was
just in the neighborhood.
Beans: That can’t be true.
Thank you very much.
Ging: I saw the old man’s video.
That pen
and the notepad over there.
- Beans: Huh?
- Ging: Can you leave one
by the phone
in the conference room for me?
Beans: Oh.
There should already be one.
Ging: All right.
Never mind, then.
And the same trash can, too?
Beans: There is.
If I may, why do you ask?
Ging: So four-- hold on.
Let’s make it eight.
Beans: Huh?
Ging: Read this.
Beans: Your rules
for the election.
Is that right?
Ging: Yeah.
Beans: But what is
this for, then?
Ging: In a few days,
this place will host
a meeting for the zodiacs.
It’ll likely end
with drawing lots.
Beans: Uh, but how
do you know that?
Ging: If we all
try to talk it out
or decide by a simple vote,
we’re not gonna get anywhere.
After all,
pariston’ll be there.
As far as he’s concerned,
1-in-12 odds
are perfectly acceptable.
All he cares about
is having the advantage.
Either way, it’s a win for him.
Beans: Oh.
Ging: Meanwhile,
everyone else will assume
that their odds are five in six,
which guarantees a drawing.
Who will it be?
Cheadle’s the favorite.
Second place, saccho.
Dark horse, piyon.
Kanzai’s the long shot.
Beans: You really think
they’ll ask me to draw?
- Are you sure?
- Ging: Who else is there?
Everyone else in this building
is in pariston’s pocket.
If these rules
look acceptable to you,
fold it three times,
and keep it until the meeting.
Beans: Eh?
Ging: But if they
don’t ask for you
or you see that I folded
my paper differently,
i’ll look down at the floor.
If you see me do that, burn it.
Beans: Mister ging,
if you would be willing
to consider becoming chairman--
ging: That’s not gonna happen.
No chance. Sorry ’bout that.
I’m not doing this
so I can change the result.
- Beans: Huh?
- Ging: All i’m doing
is following
the old man’s wishes,
and i’m definitely
not looking for any trouble.
Beans: If so,
then what of rule five?
- Ging: That’s just a decoy.
- Beans: Uh...
Ging: If I leave number five in,
it’ll make people
stop and think,
and if I agree
to concede number five,
they’ll be more willing
to accept the others.
This is how thugs
and frauds con people,
not all that special.
I’ll step down
if it passes. Deal?
Beans: Mister ging,
why would you do all of this
if not to change the result?
Ging: That’s
a pretty unusual question.
When I can make my quarry
move how I want,
i’ve succeeded as a hunter.
- ( Beans gasps )
- Ging: I just want to have
some fun with the process.
That’s all.
Narrator:
All 12 zodiacs as a group
became the election task force.
One of the zodiacs,
known as cluck,
sent ballots out
to every hunter in the world.
♪
The 13th chairman
general election.
Number of hunters, 661.
Number of nominees, the same.
Bring your ballot with you
and drop it into the ballot box
while at least three election
task force members are present
and your identification
has been verified.
The venue...
The hunter association
headquarters building.
Off-site voting is also allowed
as long as three election
task force members are present.
Voting will take place
between 12 A.M., August 8,
and 11:59 and 59 seconds P.M.
on the same day.
Of course,
strict punctuality is expected.
Off-site voting
will take place simultaneously,
regardless of time zone.
Votes will be tallied
the same day.
( Clock ticks )
It is now August eighth.
The time is 12 A.M.
The voting begins.
♪
( Hisoka chuckles )
May I put it in now?
Kanzai: Look who it is.
I didn’t expect
a cold murderer like you
to be interested
in worldly affairs.
Hisoka: 85 points.
( Chuckles ) Well, i’m not.
This is blank, you see.
( Kanzai growls )
Ginta: Then what exactly
are you doing here?
Hisoka: 90 points.
What i’m doing is trying
to find a man named ging.
Piyon: Well, i’m sorry,
but he’s gone already.
And he said that the next time
we see him here
will be at the revote,
so why don’t you, like,
take your paper and leave?
Hisoka: 77 points.
Very well.
♪
Kanzai: Huh?
You’re annoying!
Get out, would you?!
What’s the matter with you?!
Aren’t you done here?!
Hisoka: Hmph.
( Kanzai growls )
Ginta: I bet he’s
taking stock of everyone.
Hisoka: Ten points.
20 points.
45 points.
Ten points.
Two points.
50 points.
30 points.
It looks like even pro hunters
aren’t anything special.
I suppose I should
go after the zodiacs next.
( Gasps )
95 points.
( Clattering )
♪
( Beans clears throat )
I have in my hands the results
for the 13th
chairman’s election.
Valid votes, 580.
Invalid votes, 48.
Absentee, 33.
No candidates
received a majority.
The turnout, 87.7%
so as per the rules,
there must be a new vote.
Ging: Come on!
Just let me take a peek!
- Beans: Sorry, no.
- Ging: I’m only curious, okay?
Beans: I will not allow anyone
to view the ballots,
and, as the chief executive,
i’m afraid the decision
is mine and mine alone.
Ging: It’s no fun if I
can’t see who voted for who!
Meanie! Baldy!
Zodiacs: Idiot.
( Wind blowing )
Illumi: Nothing else to do?
Hisoka: The same as you.
Illumi: Something tells me
you don’t watch the news.
Hisoka: Hmm?
Illumi: We’re voting,
because chairman netero died.
Rumor has it he died fighting
a non-native species of ant
and the association was given
a big backyard as a reward.
Hisoka: Ants?
Illumi: That’s what I thought.
A lot of stuff
happened around the world
while you were off
playing tag with chrollo.
If you’d stopped to think
even for a moment,
you could have
fought the chairman
or the ants, for that matter.
My time is too precious
for those moments.
Perhaps I could use a manager.
Are you interested?
Illumi: Gon and killua
also joined in the ant hunt.
Now gon is
on the verge of death,
and killua’s
gone to see our father.
Hisoka: Wait. Come again?
Illumi: At this rate,
they’ll both die.
Hisoka: Both, did you say?
Illumi: I cannot
allow that to happen.
♪
Hisoka: Out with it.
What is it you’re talking about?
( Illumi sighs )
The zoldyck family
has another younger brother...
And I want to get rid of him.
♪
( Singing in Japanese )