Narrator: In order
to become kings,
the chimera ants
have spread across the world,
committing acts of utmost
tyranny wherever they go.
♪
Fearing further damage,
the government asks the hunter
association for their help.
Finally, the extermination
is about to begin.
( Chimera ants panting )
Human ant: Eh?
Ah!
Flutter: Eh?
♪
Shaiapouf: Ah, is that all?
I see.
( Hagya gasps )
- ( Human ant gasps )
- ( Flutter grunts )
( Hagya chuckles )
♪
( Singing in Japanese )
( Insects chirping )
( Both grunt )
Killua: Sneaking in
was pretty easy.
The only question now is how
we’re gonna get close enough
to the enemy to strike.
Gon: And it’ll be kinda tough,
since we really can’t let
just anyone see us, either.
killua: This country
secretly regulates information
using informants.
Gon: Informants?
Killua: Yeah.
Expose an enemy spy,
get a reward.
Find evidence of an uprising,
Catch a defector, get a reward.
Gon: People will do anything
for something in return?
Killua: They’re not
just after money.
When they rack up
enough informant points,
the entire group is promoted.
but you commit a crime
or you provide them false intel,
then the entire group
is given punishment.
Gon: Carrot and stick, huh?
killua: Yeah,
pretty nasty business.
Family members are split
into different groups,
so if a whole group
tries to escape
their remaining family
can be executed
or imprisoned for life.
If a family is caught
trying to escape together,
they’ll be executed on the spot.
For this country’s elite
to live the good life,
the rest of its citizens starve.
Of course, the media
is lying constantly,
making up false stories,
like, "in other countries,
half the people starve to death
before age ten."
Foreign aid never gets
to those who need it.
Instead, it’s spent on cars,
jewels, and missiles.
( Gon groaning )
Killua: I even heard that east
gorteau’s nuclear development,
which they’re using
as a bargaining chip
in international politics,
is also being funded
by foreign aid.
( Gon groaning )
killua: Hey!
Did you just blow a fuse?!
Gon: Uh, no, I think i’m okay.
that was just
a whole lot to take in.
But you sure know
a lot about it, huh?
Killua: My older brother
told me everything,
and he probably
heard it from grandpa.
Gon: Oh. Yeah?
Killua: Yeah. A long time ago,
he had to infiltrate the place
in order to finish
a job he was doing.
And I saw similar information
when I was looking around
the hunter website.
the same system
might still be in place.
( Both gasp )
♪
Gon: A town.
Killua: Yeah, a tiny one.
Gon: So what now?
Killua: We sneak in.
Gon: Are you sure
that’s a good idea?
killua: We need
up-to-date information,
like what kinda clothes
they wear here
or how to identify somebody’s
rank and social status.
They might also have
certain practices in place
to root out suspected spies.
The more data we have,
the better we are.
Wait here, okay?
Gon: It looks deserted.
Maybe everybody is already
on their way to the capital.
killua: Nuh-uh.
Something’s happened here.
Someone’s trying to hide it.
Gon: Huh?
Killua: And they did
a sloppy job, too.
( Gon grunts )
♪
( Dogs growl )
( Gon gasps )
Killua: These are
shallow graves.
Wild dogs got to the bodies.
I bet the entire village
is buried here.
Gon: But what’s going on here?
Killua: I think this is
the true purpose of the rally.
When whole towns disappear,
nobody will even be suspicious.
They set it up perfectly.
The selection has begun.
♪
in hindsight,
summoning all of the citizens
and then sorting them out
would be extremely difficult.
all told, that’s
about five million people.
Clearing out one town or city
at a time is more effective.
In that case,
their concern would just be
coworkers or family,
anyone who would
notice them missing.
But with everything going on
with the national rally,
no one will find it strange
if they can’t contact someone.
Cellphones aren’t allowed
in this nation,
so everyone would assume
they were traveling,
and not getting in touch
wouldn’t be suspicious at all.
The selection
should go smoothly.
The capital city of peijing
is in the southeast corner.
They’d need to start with
western towns and work east.
As long as the towns
all get the same story,
that the government
is assigning them each
a unique time to depart,
troublesome communication
between the villages
is less likely to be a problem.
Gon: So you’re saying
if they can prevent people
from meeting between towns
to travel together,
they can eliminate
any cause for commotion.
- But...
- Killua: Hmm?
Gon: That means they have
to run all around the country
to attack all
five million citizens, right?
Killua: Yeah.
If only 1% survives,
that gives them 50,000 soldiers.
Gon: Yeah, I know,
but I mean before that.
- Killua: What?
- Gon: There are ten--
no, there are
only nine more days left.
If you wanted to check
five million people
in that time,
then you’d probably need
a whole lot of help,
wouldn’t you?
Okay, so let’s say
that in ten days,
one nen user can check
10,000 citizens.
That’s, uh...
( Groans )
- Killua: It’s 500.
- Gon: Yeah, that!
killua: There can’t be
that many ants that can use nen.
- Is that what you’re saying?
- Gon: Yeah.
Killua: I agree with you,
but it won’t be that hard.
It isn’t like
they need nen users
in order to check everyone out.
Gon: Huh? Why not?
Killua: Manipulation.
( Gon gasps )
♪
It’s what that chimera ant used.
I’m guessing that it
can automate victims
or, like genthru’s power,
control multiple people at once.
Of course, ordinary humans
have aura as well,
so the manipulator
could force a victim’s aura
to concentrate in his fist.
One punch alone could easily
create an army of 50,000,
leaving 4,950,000 dead
in the process.
( Gon gasps )
killua: Well,
it isn’t all bad news.
If my theory’s correct,
this’ll be easy.
We just cause a commotion, and
the selection will totally stop.
We just have to pop up,
take out
whoever’s being controlled,
and cause a panic.
And then after that,
we encourage
the people who escape
to go off and check
on other nearby towns.
if the ants
have sent controlled puppets
instead of actual nen users,
this’ll all be a cinch.
You and I will just run around
taking them down
one after another
and wreaking havoc.
Gon: Right!
killua: The problem
is they’ll detect us quickly.
( Gon sighs )
Killua: Once we make our move,
they’ll know.
If we want to go through
with the old man’s plan,
then we should try
to keep as low a profile
as we possibly can.
( Gon grunts )
Killua: Your call.
Gon: Let’s do it!
if the selection
really has already begun,
we can’t just simply ignore it.
Killua: I’m with you. Let’s go.
Gon: Okay!
Killua: But i’m
gonna do it alone.
- gon: Huh?
- Killua: You stay hidden.
Gon: Stay hidden? But wouldn’t
it be better if we--
killua: Don’t forget
our primary mission.
We have to take pitou down.
( Gon gasps )
killua:
That should be your focus.
you let me handle
everything else, all right?
I’ll stir things up.
And, uh, no offense,
but this’ll be a lot easier
to do alone.
( Gon groans )
Yeah, I get it.
Killua: Do you?
Gon: Eh?
killua: Do you
really think you get it?
Gon: Killua.
killua:
Then promise me something!
Don’t make a move,
even if people are killed
right in front of you!
Promise me.
( Gon gasps )
♪
( Killua grunts )
( Gon gasps, grunts )
( Killua sighs )
I’ll text you, okay?
Our cellphones should
still work in this area.
Gon: Killua?
Killua: Sorry.
Don’t worry about it.
I’m just a little on edge.
( Chuckles )
Male: What’s this?
They’re not citizens
of this country.
That’s for sure.
They look a little young
to be spies,
but they’re definitely strong.
Assassins, maybe?
are they here
to hunt down the king?
If so, I can’t ignore them,
but I definitely don’t want
to fight both of them at once
or the silver-haired one
on the left at all.
I can tell he’s strong
by the way he walks.
He might even rival
a squadron leader.
( Gasps )
That kid is extraordinary.
I killed my presence,
but he still sensed something.
Huh?
( Laughs )
Well, that’s convenient.
( Chorus playing on phonograph )
Man: Are you sure about this?
Are you actually going
to transport my family and me
to another country?
Knov: No cause for alarm.
We have already been granted
official approval for the move,
and all necessary paperwork
is in order,
and now the only thing
that we lack is your signature.
however,
the condition that you share
your complete knowledge
of military affairs
in exchange for your freedom
is essential.
( Man grunts )
Knov: As it states
in the agreement,
if you fail to keep up your end
of the bargain after signing,
we will both find ourselves
in difficult positions.
Man: Well, that won’t be
a problem at all.
I’ll tell you everything.
( Sighs )
Everything, all of it,
all the atrocities
Diego has committed.
Morel: Yeah, thanks for that.
And don’t forget all our lives
are on the line here, too.
"Diego has committed"?
Like you’re so innocent.
The wine you’re drinking,
even the room
you’re standing in,
you only have it, because you
followed that bastard.
You mean, "we’ve committed,"
you son of a bitch.
Eh?
( Knov sighs )
Morel: But I get it.
Business is business.
Now then, Mr. Marcos,
just go on about your day
as usual.
In two weeks,
you and your family
will be relaxing on the beach.
Knuckle: I don’t like it.
( Crunching )
You really want me to turn
a blind eye to everything
while people are dying?
Oh, i’m sorry!
Am I putting you to sleep here?
Shoot: Will you please
calm yourself down?
( Knuckle growls )
look, if they plan
to sort five million citizens,
then that’s 500,000 a day,
and only 1% of them
will survive!
Shoot: Your point?
Knuckle: That means
495,000 people
have already been killed!
How can you be so damn calm?!
Shoot: Because if we
lose our cool now,
it’s a death sentence
for billions more.
( Knuckle groans )
Shoot: If this plan fails,
then everybody dies,
and if we can’t draw
the three royal guards away,
then even chairman netero
can’t defeat the king.
So no matter what,
we can’t afford to let them
discover our existence
until the time is just right.
If that happens,
security around the king
will be tightened even further.
( Knuckle growls )
Shoot: You must endure.
Knuckle: So you’re saying
sacrifice five million
to save humanity?
Shoot: That’s right.
If blaming me consoles you
at all, then go ahead,
but unless you’ve come up
with a better idea,
i would advise you
not to be too self-righteous.
Knuckle: Damn.
Shoot: We must do what we can,
and we have to put
our all into it,
even if it means our lives.
Knuckle: Yeah.
( Fruit crunches )
Gon: I hope killua’s okay.
He was acting kinda weird.
Maybe I should have
stayed with him.
But if i’d followed him,
I bet he’d be pretty mad.
( Gasps )
♪
Chimera ant: Nice job dodging.
How about this?
( Grunts )
( Growls )
( Gon gasps )
( Chimera ant laughs )
I use my strong tail as a spring
to propel me through the trees!
it’s impossible
to follow my moves in the dark!
( Laughs )
That’s right where I want you.
Now prepare to be crushed
like a tiny, little bug!
( Growls )
- ( Gon grunts )
- ( Chimera ant gasps )
Gon: You’re not crushing me.
Who has whom now, huh?!
( Chimera ant screams )
It’s a good thing he seems
to have the genes of a snake.
He should be able to go
at least ten days
without starving to death.
Meleoron: He’s strong,
just as I thought,
but i’ll
just keep watching for now.
Gon: They found me fast.
I really need to hide better.
But it’s strange.
Why are there
still soldiers ants
in an area they’ve
already finished sorting?
Maybe there are
extra lookouts here,
because we’re
pretty near the border.
♪
( Gasps )
An owl and a bat?
( Flapping )
( Meleoron laughs )
Now it’s one on two.
What ya gonna do?
Narrator: The chimera ants
use the cover of darkness
to attack gon...
And meleoron is following him.
The question is, why?
♪
( Singing in Japanese )