Knuckle: ’cause i--
I can’t see him
as just something
to exterminate now.
You heard him.
He acknowledged
how serious we were.
He wasn’t a bad guy.
( Moans )
So why would we keep doing this?
I can’t think of a reason.
Knov: The king.
The soldiers
are of no consequence.
The king can just wave his hand
and turn all of them
into evil spawn.
♪
( Singing in Japanese )
( Wind blowing )
Netero: This is a test site
for military weapons...
Which means that we won’t need
to restrain ourselves.
King: Why do you and I
have to fight?
Netero: Huh?
King: You have absolutely
no chance of defeating me.
There is no need for us
to hasten your inevitable death.
Netero: Saying I can’t win
is pretty presumptuous of you.
I can tell that you
don’t know squat about me.
( Blows )
If you judge a book
by its cover,
don’t be surprised
if you get burned.
King: You’ve got it wrong.
You don’t seem
like some ordinary man
who can’t read
the state of the battle.
I was born for one reason,
and that is to rule this world.
Originally you pathetic humans
were no more
than livestock to me,
but i’ve changed my mind.
I have since determined
that there are a few humans
that are worth keeping alive...
Like that girl, for example.
You are worthy as well.
I can sense it.
If you will back down
this instant...
Then I will consider
sparing you.
Netero: You’re saying
you would spare me
and not the others?
Is that right?
♪
Given my unique position,
I simply can’t accept
that offer.
Narrator: Meanwhile,
deep within the palace,
in exchange for his agreement
to stay still for the moment,
pouf was pressing pitou
to explain exactly
what had happened.
♪
( No audible dialogue )
Pitou complied
with pouf’s request,
telling him
what happened after the attack
and all that had transpired
since they had separated.
Pitou made it a point
to include several details
that gon did not know
to ensure that gon’s attention
would be focused
on the explanation.
But pitou, unable to describe
the events accurately,
chose not to mention
how the king had held komugi,
not knowing how to capture
the scene in words.
There was
no significant change in gon.
However...
When gon’s eyes
wavered briefly,
pitou knew the plan
had been a success.
Neferpitou: The king...
He left with the enemy
of his own volition
by that doorway.
There’s no need for us
to go after him.
Shaiapouf: Hmm.
I understand.
He went south.
Thank you for telling me.
A fine play, pitou.
Then we should stay here
and await his return.
We must be patient.
To maintain
only my outward appearance,
I only need 1/7
of my flying segments.
The other segments will go...
To the king!
King: You will fight
knowing that you cannot win?
I don’t understand.
Are you fighting me
for all of humanity?
If so, then you should
know that my actions
are entirely for their benefit.
For example, in human society,
lands are split by borders
marking their territory.
On the right side of the border,
children may starve to death,
while on the left,
idle dregs who do nothing
have everything they need.
It’s absolute madness.
I shall crush that madness
and create a fair world
where the concept of inequality
will be completely forgotten
for all time.
Netero: Hmm.
King: I don’t deny
that i’ll start
by using power and terror
to accomplish my objective,
but only when
absolutely necessary
and only to bring about order.
You see, I have learned
what true power
is meant to be used for...
( No audible dialogue )
To protect the weak
who deserve to live.
That is its purpose.
Power shouldn’t be used
to torment the defeated.
♪
Netero: This is
quite the situation.
King: I will not fight
with you now.
I left the palace
so we could have a discussion.
We need to have a free
and uninhibited conversation.
Netero: Well,
he’s beginning to waver.
King: Come closer.
Netero: Wavering
between ant and human,
yet it seems
he hasn’t yet realized
that those two sides
are totally incompatible.
And as of now,
neither one is dominant.
He’ll fall to one or the other,
but either way, the outcome
will remain the same.
♪
Man: We’re counting on you.
You have only
one mission to carry out,
the immediate execution of all
of these dangerous creatures.
Netero: There have already
been many casualties.
We will proceed
using any means necessary.
Will that be acceptable to you?
Man: Well, don’t ask me.
We wouldn’t dream of telling
the experts how to proceed.
All we desire now is
for those dangerous creatures
to be eradicated as swiftly
and humanely as possible.
Netero: Yes, of course.
I understand.
So their goal
is to eradicate the ants,
leaving the hunter association
to take the blame.
I get it.
( Wind blowing )
I’m going to need
to make this fast...
Before my heart is swayed.
Look, king...
We’ve all got problems,
you know.
( King gasps )
♪
Netero:
100-type guanyin bodhisattva!
First hand!
( Wind blowing )
( Wings fluttering )
( Shaiapouf gasps )
Is that...
♪
Menthuthuyoupi: I can’t sense
anyone else fighting here.
Does that mean
that i’m the only one left?
Shaiapouf: Youpi!
Menthuthuyoupi: Huh? Huh?!
Pouf! You’ve changed a lot
since the last time I saw you.
Shaiapouf: I suppose I could
say the same thing about you.
I had to be careful
and escape from there
without alerting the enemy.
If I moved
all my particles at once,
it would have been suspicious,
so I moved slowly.
I’m sure you’re rushed,
but could you spare a moment?
I need to tell you
what’s been happening.
Menthuthuyoupi: Yeah.
I suppose i’ve got a minute.
Guess everyone
does have their reasons.
Shaiapouf: Uh...
You sound so grown up.
And there you have it.
I hope pitou’s change
will benefit the king...
But I can’t be sure.
I’ve no conclusive proof
one way or the other.
♪
Narrator: Based on
his own experiences,
youpi could understand
pitou’s behavior.
- Shaiapouf: Youpi...
- Menthuthuyoupi: Eh?
Shaiapouf: So tell me.
What do you think
we should do now?
Narrator: He was being tested.
This tactic
made it quite clear to youpi
that pouf was afraid,
unnerved by the subtle changes
that both pitou and youpi
had only recently undergone.
( Menthuthuyoupi scoffs )
A dumb question.
( Grunts )
♪
There’s no time to waste.
We must go to the king...
And that’s all there is to it.
Am I right?
Narrator:
His response was sincere.
Shaiapouf: Indeed, you are.
Narrator: Only one thing
concerned him at the moment,
and that was leaving
as quickly as possible...
Because the fear
that gripped pouf
had taken hold of youpi as well.
♪
Netero: I’m sure
that was a direct hit.
He’s a tough one.
King: A very good attack.
I wasn’t expecting it.
( Wind blowing )
Are you satisfied?
Netero: He still wants me
to sit with him?
King: I will not repeat myself.
♪
Netero: Third hand!
I cannot back down any longer.
( Gasps )
( Creaking )
♪
King: Are you really
so eager to die?
Narrator:
From the king’s perspective,
the wrath that was unleashed
was unimpressive,
seemingly no stronger than that
of a child throwing a tantrum,
but the king’s full power
was violent enough
to make netero jump back more
than twice his usual distance.
Netero couldn’t help but feel
insulted by this turn of events
and by the fact
that his determination,
strong as it was,
could be brushed off so easily.
King: Wake up.
Can’t you see words are all that
you and I will exchange here?
You should save your energy.
Netero: Damned newborn brat.
If it were that simple,
I wouldn’t have to do this.
Wait.
Exchanging words?
Hey, king...
Would you like
to know your name?
King: How is it that you have
come into possession of my name?
Netero: Simple, really.
My subordinates were present
at your mother’s deathbed.
She uttered your name
with her dying breath.
I bet i’m the only one
who knows now those
same subordinates probably died
fighting your royal guard.
( Wind blowing )
Are you interested
in fighting me now?
I’ll make you a deal.
If you can force me
to admit defeat,
i’ll tell you your name.
King: Force you?
But without killing you?
( Scoffs )
So i’ll be playing
without a rook and bishop.
♪
Fine, then.
I’ll checkmate you shortly.
♪
Narrator: The real battle
between netero and the king
has begun.
( Singing in Japanese )