Ikalgo: All I know is this--
you looked at a good-for-nothing
octopus like me,
and you said I was cool.
you even said
we could have been friends.
I can’t stand by while you die!
I’m gonna save you!
Don’t you die on me!
♪
( Singing in Japanese )
Narrator: While killua
was in the process
of being rescued
by the chimera ant ikalgo,
a creature he had thought
was his enemy,
gon was forming a bond as well
with a chimera ant
who goes by the name meleoron.
( Lighter flicks )
Gon: You should really
stop smoking, you know.
Meleoron: Huh?
gon: The smoke
will stick to your clothes,
and people
will smell you coming,
which kind of defeats
the purpose
of you being invisible,
doesn’t it?
( Meleoron laughs )
I appreciate the tip,
but honestly,
it doesn’t really matter much.
while my invisibility
is sort of like my trademark,
my real ability
goes one step further.
Gon: What?
Meleoron: Here. I’ll show you.
( Inhales )
( Gasping )
What the--he’s gone.
I can’t sense him at all,
only the smell of cigarettes.
He’s not here.
this is more
than just invisibility.
Does he also have the ability
to change locations instantly
without even making a sound?
That’s impossible,
so how did he do it?
( Gasps ) Whoa!
Where did you come from?
Meleoron: Hmm? I’ve been
right here the whole time.
( Gon gasps )
Meleoron: My second ability
is perfect plan.
Whenever I hold my breath,
it prevents anyone around me
from sensing my presence,
even a little bit.
You were touching me and didn’t
even realize you were doing it.
Your mind simply refused
to acknowledge
what your eyes couldn’t see.
Gon: Huh? I really touched you?
Meleoron: You know how
some guys never get noticed?
Like the guy the waitress skips
over when you go out to eat
in a big group
at a chain restaurant?
It’s like that,
but more extreme.
i’m right here,
but no one ever notices me.
Gon: Uh...
Meleoron: Turning invisible
really is just a decoy.
it helps me
keep my true ability
a secret from everyone else.
And that’s just between
you and me, of course.
Nobody else knows,
so let’s just keep it
that way, all right?
( Gon gasps )
why tell me
something so important?
Meleoron: Well, i’ve gotta earn
your trust, don’t I?
Yeah, it’s kind of a risk,
but it’s one I have to take.
See, if I can’t
get you to trust me,
then we won’t be able
to start anything.
Gon: You mean how you said i’d
be a valuable partner, right?
Meleoron: That’s right,
but let’s hold off on that
for right now.
Gon: Eh?
Meleoron: Like I said before,
we have to trust
each other first.
Once you’ve agreed
to be my partner,
i’ll be happy to tell you
everything you want to know.
Gon: Okay. I’ll be your partner.
( Meleoron chuckles )
That was fast!
you don’t know
how to negotiate, kid!
Cut the trusting crap!
You should be suspicious of me,
of the whole world!
think about it
before you trust anyone!
Gon: Huh? I said it’s fine.
Why are you being such a drag?
Meleoron: Besides,
are you even able
to make this decision
all by yourself?!
What about your buddy?!
Isn’t he gonna have a fit
when he finds out
you teamed up with
a suspicious-looking monster?!
( Groans )
why the hell am I
trashing myself like this?
it’s not like
I chose to be this way.
Gon: He sure is restless.
( Meleoron sighs )
I guess it doesn’t matter.
Even a good friend
you’ve had for 20 years
could still
stab you in the back.
Time is not a matter of trust.
You feel me?
( Groans )
You’re not much fun, huh?
We could never be friends.
( Gon thinking )
I feel the same way.
meleoron: Well,
are you sure about this?
Gon: What?
meleoron:
About teaming up with me.
Won’t your buddy object?
Gon: Hmm. Yeah, probably.
Killua’s pretty cautious
about everything.
Meleoron: Then we’re done.
This deal is dead in the water.
Gon: Nah. It’s fine.
I’ll just insist
on having it my way.
Killua won’t like it,
but he’ll give in.
Meleoron: Well, there you go.
Kid’s got his work
cut out for him.
Whatever. If you say it’s okay,
I trust you,
so let’s get down to business.
Gon: Sure.
Meleoron: I wanna...
Take down the king.
Wanna know why?
Gon: Well, yeah. Of course I do.
That’s what i’ve
been waiting for.
Meleoron: I’m taking revenge.
( Gon gasps )
Meleoron: I can’t tell you
any of the details
on why I want revenge right now.
Gon: Okay. I’m kinda curious
about it, but I can wait.
that’s probably
what you want me to say.
( Meleoron sighs )
If you insist, I guess
i’ll have to tell you.
Gon: What?! Already?!
Meleoron: I’m just kidding.
beg all you want,
but I won’t tell you yet.
Gon: I didn’t beg
for anything.
( Lighter flicks )
( Meleoron exhales )
The king killed
someone who saved me.
His name was Peggy.
I saw the king behead him
right before my eyes.
( Gon gasps )
Meleoron: But at the time,
I didn’t even realize
that someone who was
close to me had died.
Gon: Huh? Why not?
You just said you saw it happen.
meleoron: Because i’d
forgotten who Peggy was to me.
I’d forgotten that he
was my foster father.
♪
I remembered only recently.
Memories of my human days
came flooding back.
Not all of it, of course.
Well, that’s not quite right.
there isn’t much
that I remembered at all,
my parents’ names
and my own name,
bits of my childhood.
Peggy was the name
of the chimera ant
that the king killed,
and that was also
my foster father’s human name.
He was an academic,
always carrying thick books
with him everywhere.
In his previous life,
he carried a copy
of the ngl Bible with him
all the time.
Gon: Do all the ants have
human memories like you do?
Meleoron: I don’t know
if we’re all the same.
Some chimera ants are
obviously feral in nature,
which makes it
virtually impossible
to tell what they’re thinking.
Gon: Then, I think I get it now.
Meleoron: Eh?
I think i’m finally
starting to understand
why I felt I could
trust you so quickly.
It’s ’cause you seem so human,
more human than all
the other ants i’ve met so far.
In fact, I would even say
that you’re still a human.
Meleoron: Really?
When I met you,
i had exactly
the opposite reaction.
Gon: Eh?
Meleoron: I could
immediately sense
an inhuman beast
lurking deep within you.
That’s why I wanted
to team up with you,
because we’re not all
that different, you and I.
all right.
Let’s get right to it, then.
But before we do that,
I should know your name.
I just forgot to ask.
Gon: Oh, right.
I’m gon freecss.
Meleoron: I actually
have one more ability,
and we just met
the condition to activate it.
( Gon gasps )
Meleoron: Time to show you
my third ability.
( Gon gasps )
♪
Meleoron: Activate!
Huh.
( Bird chirping )
Gon: It isn’t flying away.
( Meleoron exhales )
- ( Bird tweeting )
- ( Gon gasps )
Wait a second.
Does that mean I was using
your perfect plan, too?
Meleoron: That’s exactly right,
and the name of my third power
is god’s accomplice.
While perfect plan is activated,
it allows anyone else I touch
to use it
the very same way I do.
♪
Now do you understand
how powerful this is?
This ability will allow us
to approach and attack
an unsuspecting enemy,
and they won’t see it coming.
No matter how powerful
the king is,
one mega-punch to his
unguarded vitals, and he’s done.
( Gon shudders )
Meleoron: Hey, gon,
you’re just the perfect partner
i’ve been looking for.
If we work together,
we can deal that son of a bitch
an unprecedented blow.
So I was watching you
back when you used
that jan-Ken-rock thing.
- Those were my men, you know.
- ( Gon gasps )
Meleoron: I sent them
to attack so I could see
how much strength
you were working with,
and you saw how that went.
Uh, but no need to feel bad.
As it turns out,
those bastards were killing
for fun behind my back.
They’re not my soldiers
or my allies anymore.
well, I guess
from their perspective,
i’m the one who changed,
not them.
Gon: About being your partner...
i’m just not
the partner you want.
Meleoron: You know
someone who’d be better?
Gon: I sure do.
I’ll contact him.
Meleoron: Hold on.
Right or wrong, I do trust you.
And if you end up betraying me,
I won’t blame you,
and I won’t even
regret my decision,
because I watched you,
and I spoke to you,
and it was my choice
to trust you,
but i’m not about to place
my trust in someone else
just because you trust them.
That’s not how
this is gonna work.
That make sense to you?
Gon: Mm-hmm. I get your point,
but still--
meleoron: Hey, it’s my life
on the line here, right?
Listen. My perfect plan’s
not invincible at all.
It’s actually more vulnerable
than you might think.
Nobody is aware of me
or my existence,
but i’m still right there
in the same place.
It isn’t like
i’ve gone anywhere.
It’s just they
may not notice me,
but their attacks
can still hit me.
if an enemy knew
that they were in the same room
as somebody with my ability,
what would they do then?
They’d launch attacks
in every direction.
( Gon gasps )
Yeah, you’re right.
meleoron: If one
of those attacks hit me,
even by dumb luck,
i’d be done for.
hate to say it,
but when it comes to combat,
i’m the weakest
chimera ant around.
I’m basically a foot soldier.
Forget the king.
I couldn’t even survive a punch
from a squadron leader.
If I just turn invisible,
I can be located with en.
It’s already been tested,
so the other squadron leaders
know it, too.
I need my enemies to believe
that my power is weak.
They need to think
just a little bit of en
is enough to beat it.
so the only way
this ability is invincible
is if no one knows it exists
in the first place.
But enough explaining.
my point is that
I don’t want to reveal my power
to anyone else, not even
if it’s someone you trust.
You understand?
Gon: Find out for yourself.
Meleoron: Huh?
Gon: I’ll call him over,
but I won’t mention
that you’re here.
- ( Cell phone beeps )
- Meleoron: Hey, wait.
Gon: You can watch things
from a distance.
( Phone line ringing )
- Gon: Hi. It’s--
- knuckle: Hey!
I’ve been waiting, idiot.
You pulled a fast one.
where are you?
i’ve got lots
of questions for you.
The boss had to make a move
because of you two kids.
The original plan’s
been completely derailed,
but I approve of what
you’re doing out there.
( Gon gasps )
Knov: We can’t just let
five million innocent people
die like that.
The boss already
used his ability
to surround the capital.
Gon: Really?
knuckle: Yeah.
That should make it harder
for neferpitou to use
their ability remotely,
so they’re not going to be able
to perform any kind
of long-distance sorting.
Gon: Right.
Knuckle: However,
the boss and Mr. Knov
will be expending all their
energy to delay neferpitou,
which means,
when the operation begins,
they’re not gonna be
in any condition
to take on the royal guards.
( Gon sighs )
Knuckle: We fully expect
that more citizens
will gather in the capital
for the celebration.
There might still be a massacre.
the situation
hasn’t gotten any less grim.
We can’t contact
the chairman anymore.
he’s focusing and
honing his energy somewhere,
waiting for zero hour.
♪
the four of us
need to make a choice.
Do we summon reinforcements
or face the three royal guards
all by ourselves?
( Gon groans )
Knuckle: What does killua
think about it?
Gon: He’s not here.
Knuckle: Are you saying
that you two split up?
oh, I get it.
He was doing all this himself.
Can you call him?
( Busy signal beeping )
Gon: Sorry. He’s not picking up.
His phone is off.
Knuckle: That so? Well,
don’t give up. Keep trying.
we should all
touch base real soon,
- and the sooner, the better.
- Gon: Yeah.
Knuckle: We need to find
a halfway point for us
where we can meet up
when we can.
Shoot: Mm.
Knuckle: Here. Mandai city.
Gon: Right. Got it.
( Hangs up )
♪
King: Checkmate.
You’re finished.
( Man stammering )
King: Now, why didn’t
you concede defeat?
Man: Uh...
( Wincing )
king: Do not
make me repeat myself.
The match was decided
22 moves ago.
so then tell me
why you didn’t concede.
Did you actually think
that I would make a mistake?
( Man gasping )
( Yelps )
King: The fool.
Shaiapouf: Next we have
the national go champion.
King: Hand over the rule book.
Shaiapouf: It looks simple,
but it’s a very complex game.
It may take even more time
to learn than shogi.
♪
Champion: Please, let me go!
What do you want?!
Someone, anyone, help me!
( Groans )
My glasses.
Shaiapouf: Silence.
You are in the presence
of the king.
( Champion gasping )
King: The choice is yours.
You will either
sit across from me,
or you will die.
( Game piece clatters )
Shaiapouf: 5 1/2 points.
The king wins.
champion:
It only took him 10 games?
I’m just tired, that’s all.
That’s why I lost.
I might have a slight fever.
I’m really dizzy and weak.
King: Take eight hours
and medicine.
I want you in top condition.
Lose again, and I won’t be
interested in your excuses,
so rest like you mean it.
Shaiapouf: I’m impressed
by how quickly you learn.
these games
are quite difficult.
I’m shocked that it took you
less than half the time
it took to learn shogi.
king: I just learned
the trick to it. That was all.
chess, go, shogi,
the rules may be different,
but every first-rate player
has a certain rhythm
to his play.
The key is to disrupt
their rhythm
and therefore their game.
As soon as you learn the basics,
you can deduce their rhythm...
♪
And once you know their rhythm,
disrupting it is easy.
shaiapouf:
A psychological approach
that would apply
to any contest.
So now that you’ve learned this,
I fail to see the benefit
of further games.
I believe they will
only serve to bore you.
King: Mm.
What else remains?
Shaiapouf: Just one more game
is played here professionally.
It’s a board game
that they call gungi.
King: What is that?
Shaiapouf: Seems the game
began in east gorteau,
and nearly all the citizens
there know how to play it.
King: Give me the rule book.
shaiapouf:
The goal is to checkmate
your opponent’s king,
as in chess.
However, pieces can be
stacked up to three high,
and the opening formation
of pieces is variable.
it requires
three-dimensional thinking,
making it somewhat different
from other board games
of this nature.
World tournaments have
been held around the globe
each of the last 15 years,
and, in all that time,
east gorteau has yet to lose.
they are now
on their third representative,
who is a five-time
reigning champion.
King: Hmm.
So then if I defeat
this champion,
i’ll be the best in the world?
A fitting end to this diversion.
Call them.
(Cane tapping)
Narrator: Six days left
until the sorting.
A young girl appears who will
shape the fate of the king.
But in what way, exactly...
He has no idea at all.
♪
( Singing in Japanese )