( Waves crashing )
Phinks: Right.
So where are we on the island?
Let’s steal an accompany card
so we can go somewhere.
( Gasps )
Man: Uninvited guests, huh?
( Spiders grunt )
Man: Hmm.
Makes me nervous.
Just to be sure,
you folks aren’t castaways,
are you?
I doubt it, since the strong
currents around the island
make it virtually impossible
to drift here by accident.
Phinks: This guy’s tough.
Who the hell are you?
You supposed to be
our guide or something?
Man: No, i’m just one
of the creators of this game.
You can call me razor.
I mainly handle
the emissive systems,
like, uh, traveling by spell
- and trespassers.
- ( Spiders gasp )
Razor: This spell can only
be used by a gamemaster.
Sorry, but you’ll have to leave.
Come back the right way,
and you’ll be welcome here.
There’s an excellent item
in the game
that you can obtain
by fighting me,
so if you decide to play,
we’ll probably
get to fight eventually.
Phinks: Fine, then.
We’ll be right back
through the front door
next time.
Razor: Eliminate on.
Huh. That’s one
intimidating group of people.
I can tell you that. Hmm?
( Grunts )
♪
( Singing in Japanese )
Narrator: As gon continues
to train, he discovers a hint
to developing
his ultimate technique.
Gon: Show me rock! Come on!
Jan Ken rock!
Killua: Whoa!
Bisky: I see.
Gon: Next up!
All right.
Show me rock.
Jan Ken paper!
- ( Boing )
- ( Music stops )
Bisky, how do I make my nen fly?
( Killua groans )
Bisky: Train more.
Killua: Paper’s
an emitter technique?
Gon: Uh-huh.
And scissors is a transmuter.
Pretty soon, I want to try
to cut through a rock.
Bisky: Understood.
That’s a reasonable
fighting technique.
But a childish idea.
Gon: I can focus my nen
in my fist,
but you know
how it takes a lot of time?
I was trying to figure out
a good way
that I could spend that time.
When you were talking
about the game, it just hit me,
’cause I like that game.
Bisky: Hmph. It’s important
to trust in your instincts.
Those gut feelings
play a big role
in techniques that require
multiple categories.
The real key is that it
should feel right to you.
- Killua: Uh, ahem.
- Bisky: Hmm?
Gon: Hmm?
( Both gasp )
Killua: Well, this is
all i’ve got right now,
but if I charge it up,
it’s pretty strong.
Gon: That’s awesome, killua!
You’re like an electric eel!
Killua: Awful analogy.
- Come on, man.
- Gon: What?
Bisky: He can change aura
into electricity at his age?
It’s frightening,
not to mention tragic.
His childhood must have
been a living hell.
In fact, it’s a miracle that he
can smile at all anymore.
♪
Mm, look at them.
They make such a great team.
Hmm. Well, what do you say?
Shall we call it a day?
Killua: Huh?
Bisky: It’s a bit early,
- but how ’bout a party?
- Killua: Party?
Bisky: What do you boys do
to celebrate back home?
- Gon: Celebrate?
- ( Bisky giggles )
It’s almost new year’s
in the real world, isn’t it?
Time flows at the same speed
in here as it does outside.
- ( Gon gasps ) Oh, no!
- Killua: Hmm?
Gon: I forgot! The deadline
for the hunter exam’s coming up!
Killua: Oh, man.
And right when training
was starting to get
kind of fun, too.
Bisky: If my memory serves,
you have to apply by year’s end.
Gon: Then we need to hurry!
But remind me
how we get outside again.
Killua: I’m guessing
there are spell cards
to leave the game, right?
Bisky: There are, so let’s take
another trip to masadora.
Boys: All right!
Bisky: Now let’s find
a place to have some tea.
Gon: We can’t.
We don’t have much time.
Killua: We can ask
at the stores we go to.
Shopkeeper: You want
to leave the island?
No sweat.
That’ll be 3,000 Jenny.
- ( Killua groans )
- ( Gon grunts )
Shopkeeper: If you go
about 50 kilometers west,
you’ll reach
the island’s only port.
You’ll have to defeat
or bribe the harbor master.
If you do, you’ll get a ticket
that’ll transport you outside.
Gon: How big of a bribe
do you think?
Shopkeeper: That depends
on how he’s feeling.
Killua: Yeah, okay.
Shopkeeper: Your other option
is to use a leave spell card,
but that one
is pretty rare, so...
Gon: What do we do?
Killua: Head to the port.
Since its a rare card,
it might not even show up,
no matter how much we spend.
Gon: Yeah, you’re right.
( Seabirds calling )
( Electricity crackles )
( Glass shatters )
Both: Hmm?
Killua: Voila.
Killua: Heh. Well,
I guess now i’ll go ace the exam
and come right back.
Gon: First go
to the lone cedar tree
that’s down by dolle harbor.
Magical beasts called kiriko
live there.
Just tell them
that you’re my friend,
and they’ll take you
right to the exam site.
Killua: Will do. See ya.
♪
Bisky: All right, then.
Let’s get back to your training.
Gon: Osu!
Woman: Welcome, sir.
Killua, thinking:
Is this where I started?
No, it’s not.
The girl looks familiar, though.
But that’s pretty typical
for games.
Woman: Will you be leaving
the island now?
If so, please specify
your location.
Killua: Do you have
dolle harbor?
Woman: Yes, I do.
Killua: Then just send me there.
Woman: I understand.
When you leave this island,
all of the cards
that are in your free slots
will be deleted instantly.
Do you accept that?
Killua: Yeah, that’s fine.
Woman: Well, in that case,
we will be patiently awaiting
your return, sir.
Killua: Guess i’m back
in the real world now, huh?
Doesn’t feel any different.
And book.
So it doesn’t work out here.
Gotcha.
I’ll submit my application
and head for that cedar tree.
But first i’ve
gotta shower and change.
Bisky: Okay.
We’ll train
the whole time you’re running.
When you can form
numbers zero through nine,
all within one minute, you pass.
( Gon grunting )
Bisky: Huh?
Gon: That hurt!
( Groans )
Bisky: What in the world
are you doing?!
- ( Whooshing )
- Huh?
Aren’t you...
Player: I can see that your
other friend isn’t with you.
Bisky: What’s that thing
on your shoulder?
What happened to you?
Is something wrong?
( Timer beeping )
Player: The bomber got us.
Hear me out.
I have something to say.
( Birds squawk )
Bisky: So he was the bomber.
Player: The others
are back in our hideout
waiting for him
to disarm the bombs.
They believe
in the terms he gave them,
but i’m not as convinced.
Gon: Now what? What can we do?
Bisky: If they’re prepared
to accept casualties--
- player: Won’t happen.
- ( Both gasp )
Player: The very first ones
to jump him
will be the first ones
to be sacrificed.
Who would
ever volunteer for that?
Gon: Good point.
Player: Jispa was the most
proficient of us in combat,
yet he was beaten instantly.
We were already doomed
at that point.
And allowing genthru
to leave the game
proved to be a fatal mistake.
We foolishly began to celebrate
before we had
the chance to verify
each member’s cards
and assigned roles,
and that was when
he caught us off guard.
I hate to say it,
but i--i was so distracted
that I simply didn’t see him
use leave until it was too late.
Bisky: You were probably
focused on his explanation,
trying to figure out
its meaning.
Player: Yeah. We were
thrust into that situation
with absolutely
no warning at all.
Of course, we were all
too stunned to take any action.
Bisky: I see, but may I ask why
you’re telling us all this?
♪
Player: Out of everyone
i’ve met here on the island,
I believe you’re the ones
I can rely on the most.
If you communicate
with any other players,
I beg you to tell them all
about the bomber.
If they know about his ability,
they can guard against it.
And if it comes down to it,
I want you to try to avenge us.
At the very least,
do not let him clear the game.
( Gon grunts )
Bisky: We understand.
Player: Thank you.
I’ll use what little time
I have left
to tell as many as I can
about the bomber.
Book.
Return on!
Bunzen!
( Whooshing )
Actually,
the truth of the matter
is that when I used
magnetic force,
those two were
the only players I could find.
But flattery works wonders.
When it comes
to deactivating someone’s nen,
every thousandth
of a percent counts.
Now, then...
Nickes has probably gone off
to meet with the bombers.
However, if what they promised
turns out to be
a mass detonation...
Better get started.
Genthru: You’re finally here.
Now hand over your ring.
Nickes: Jispa has passed away.
Genthru: That’s nice.
- Your ring?
- ( Nickes sputters )
Disarm everyone’s bombs first!
Genthru: Hell, no.
First I have to take that ring
back inside the game,
and once I do,
i’ll confirm that all the cards
are indeed in the binder.
Then i’ll disarm the bombs.
This is the last time.
Hand over the ring.
♪
( Nickes groans )
Genthru: Sub, go ahead,
and put it on.
If you put on a second ring
when you’re outside the game,
your original data
gets overwritten.
Sub: Mm-hmm.
Genthru: Now then,
let’s head back inside together.
Hold on.
What’s your name again?
( Nickes growls )
( Chorus vocalizing )
( Player speaking
foreign language )
Spirits of the forest,
remove the unclean nen
that is now possessing my body.
Now, what will it be, I wonder.
I call upon the power
of the forest spirits
and combine it with my own
to create a nen beast
capable of consuming
the nen abilities of others.
( Beast growling )
Player: It’s a big one.
As I feared, the bomber’s
countdown is a powerful nen.
Player #2: So how’d it go?
Player #3: Did he
disarm them yet?
Sub: Now book.
Genthru: Okay.
81 specified-slot card types.
They’re here, all right.
Nickes: Look, we did
everything you wanted,
so now disarm all the bombs!
Genthru: But of course.
I’m a man of my word.
But first, you need
to hand over three leave cards.
( Nickes gasps )
♪
Genthru: Okay, then.
Looks like we have a deal.
Sub, bara.
( Beast grumbling )
( Players gasping )
Genthru: Here goes.
Bombers: Release!
( Players sigh )
( Screaming )
♪
( Genthru laughs )
I just released all of you...
From your fear.
( Bombers laugh )
( Nickes gasps ) That...
Wasn’t our deal.
Genthru: Hmm?
You’re all losers,
and I don’t keep promises
to losers.
"Release" doesn’t disarm.
It’s the trigger word.
( Bombers laughing )
Leave on!
( Player #1 sighs )
At least now I don’t have
to worry about exploding.
- ( Beast grumbling )
- Player #1: Huh?
But i’m stuck with this guy
until genthru
reverses his ability or dies.
I’ve got myself
a troublesome companion.
Hey, be still.
The bomber’s
going to kill us all.
He’ll assume he succeeded.
I’ll use it to my advantage.
( Bird squawks )
Gon: Bisky?
Bisky: Hmm?
Gon: I think we should go
drop by their hideout real fast.
Bisky: Time’s probably
already up for them.
Besides, he didn’t even
tell us where it is.
And even if we could find it,
we’d still need a spell card
that could take us there,
and we simply don’t have one.
Gon: I know,
but some of them could have
survived the explosion.
It’s possible.
Bisky: But doubtful.
If the bomber’s powerful enough
to place bombs on his targets
without them noticing,
he’d never be that careless.
- ( Gon sighs )
- Bisky: However...
If we just continue
to play the game,
then we’re bound to run into
the bomber at some point.
And given that fact,
then sooner or later, we may
need to visit their hideout.
( Gon grunts )
Bisky: But we
still need spell cards.
Let’s go to masadora and sell
our monster cards to buy some.
Gon: Yeah! ( Laughs )
Hey, bisky,
how long do you think
it’ll take me
to master my signature move?
Bisky: Well, you are just
starting to develop your nen.
Hard to say when
your power and speed will peak.
Gon: It is?
Bisky: That said,
i’d be more than
a little bit surprised
if it took you very long
to get the form down.
Gon: Really? How long?
Bisky: Let me see. Hmm.
You may have it ready
by the time killua’s back.
( Gon grunts )
All right!
I can’t wait to see the look
on his face when he sees it.
♪
Shopkeeper:
You two are so lucky.
We just recently received
a huge shipment
of different spell cards.
Gon: So these are the ones
they’ve been hoarding.
We bought 60 between us,
so there are all kinds
of types here.
( Bisky gasps )
Gon, look.
Gon: Hmm? ( Gasps )
An s-rank!
There are only 10
in the whole game.
Bisky: What do you think?
Save it, or should we
use it right now?
Gon: Hey, don’t ask me!
I don’t know what to do!
Bisky: Shh. Be quiet.
Do you want people
getting suspicious?
( Gon groans )
If only killua was still here.
( Killua sneezes )
( Sighs )
( Kiriko father sniffing )
Well, you certainly do
smell like gon.
Kiriko mother: I miss that kid.
Kiriko father: We’ll take you
to the exam site.
Just leave it to us.
Killua: Let’s hurry.
I need to ace it
and then hurry back to gon
right away.
Kiriko mother:
Sure, but the exam
won’t officially start
for a few days.
Killua: Oh, yeah, that’s right.
Kiriko mother: In the meantime,
why don’t you tell us all
about your adventures with gon?
Killua: Okay. Well,
there was that one time
that he came to my house.
♪
Gon: Hah!
Bisky: You’re making
steady progress, gon.
You’re right on track to have
your ultimate technique ready.
Gon: It helps that this is
such a safe place to practice.
With this view,
we can spot anyone
before they get close enough
to use an attack spell.
People are watching
from masadora.
I feel it like I felt people
watching us at the start point.
But this time, we’ve got
plenty of attack spells.
Bisky: Hmm.
Yes, but just to be safe,
I already cast
a blackout curtain card.
- Gon: Mm.
- Bisky: Still...
There’s no real point
in worrying about spell cards.
You just focus
on training your hardest.
Gon: Osu!
♪
Bisky: Right.
It’s been a minute.
Next.
( Gon gasps )
Aw, man,
it didn’t reach far enough.
Bisky: Don’t worry. You’re
definitely in far better shape
than a transmuter would be.
Be patient.
Focus on maintaining
the shape of your aura.
If you can do it
for an extended period of time,
- you’re all set.
- Gon: Osu!
Bisky: The longer
you can maintain that sphere,
the stronger your ten is.
And once you’ve
trained long enough
and put in some real effort,
you’ll be able to maintain
an aura sphere
for two or three days
at a time.
You should get to where
you can reach that rock
by the end of the day.
( Gon grunts )
- ( Crack )
- ( Gasps )
You’re right! I got it!
Bisky: That was quick.
This proves
that he’s been working hard
on his ten and ren every day.
All right.
Let’s go back
to practicing the basics.
Gon: Osu!
♪
Narrator: Gon continues
to train with bisky
to master
his signature technique.
Killua has temporarily
left the game
to retake the hunter exam.
The boys, each in their own way,
are working hard
to reach their goals.
( Singing in Japanese )