♪
( Footsteps crunching )
Hisoka: So where’s
your friend?
Shalnark: Machi and nobu
are tailing him.
He’s up ahead.
Phinks:
We’re planning to let you
negotiate with the exorcist.
Price is no object,
but no matter what,
he’s gotta agree.
Hisoka: I understand.
My fight with chrollo
is on the line.
♪
( Singing in Japanese )
Nobunaga: That’s him.
Hisoka: And how
did you locate him?
Nobunaga: Yeah, as if
we’d tell you that, idiot.
( Hisoka chuckles )
You there,
hiding in the shadows...
( Both gasp )
Hisoka: Was it
with your ability?
Nobunaga:
You didn’t even use en.
What are you,
some kind of freak?
( Hisoka chuckles )
No, I just completed
a very entertaining battle.
It seems the rush
has left me very sensitized.
I should probably calm
my arousal,
and nothing relaxes me more
than ravaging someone
whom i’ve never even met.
Nobunaga: Damn it.
Machi: Come on out.
Kalluto: Was my zetsu
not good enough?
Machi: No,
it was perfect as always.
Nobunaga: He’s just
insanely perceptive.
This is troupe member four,
your replacement, as it were.
Kalluto: I am kalluto.
I won’t explain my power,
but we did find him
by using it.
Hisoka: Ah.
You look quite tasty as well.
Nobunaga: Careful.
Machi: This one
goes after anything.
Nobunaga: Hisoka,
you had better make this work.
Hisoka: You people
are so tedious.
I will, but for my own benefit.
Machi: Are you’re serious
about fighting the boss?
Hisoka: Of course.
Who would you prefer survive,
myself or your dear chrollo?
Machi: That’s stupid.
Once you finish the job here,
you can die, for all I care.
Hisoka: And if I kill chrollo,
what then?
Machi: Impossible.
But if you must know...
I’d hunt you down,
and i’d kill you.
Hisoka: Hmm.
Sounds good to me.
♪
Tsezguerra: Our primary
objective is to obtain
the angel’s breath that
team genthru has monopolized.
We have to force them
to transform a card.
If we don’t succeed,
we won’t have a chance
to use our voucher.
Barry: And that’s where
team gon comes in, isn’t it?
Tsezguerra: Mm-hmm.
While they may not have
the strength to win outright,
they’re likely
to deal serious damage
to a member of team genthru.
If they use even one
of the angel’s breaths
in their possession,
our voucher will transform
into an angel’s breath,
and then...
Barry: We’ll only need
wild luck alexandrite!
Rodriot: And if
we can just manage
to buy three weeks
for those kids,
they’ll trade the card to us,
and we’re all set!
Tsezguerra: Correct.
All right, it’s time. Let’s go.
Genthru: I believe I told you
to come alone, didn’t I?
Tsezguerra: We couldn’t
make a unanimous decision,
so we all discussed it
on our way over here,
and now we’ve
finally reached a consensus.
Genthru: Oh?
Tsezguerra: We choose battle!
♪
All: Right! Levy on!
Tsezguerra: Accompany on!
To antokiba!
( Bara and sub gasp )
Genthru: And book.
Check your cards.
Both: Book!
Sub: It’s okay.
They just got some trash
from my free slots.
Bara: Same on my end.
Genthru: Nothing
important’s missing.
Bara: That settles it.
Sub: We’ll kill ’em, yeah?
Genthru: They’ll put up a fight.
I don’t know
what just happened, but...
Their resolve was written
all over their faces.
Goreinu: Six copies
of accompany, 24 of return,
nine of drawbridge,
and two of magnetic force.
I spent all the money
I had on them.
Barry: Right.
Meet in three days.
You can use that time
to earn some more money
and buy all the cards we need.
Goreinu: Right. You got it.
Barry: Do you think
they’ll try to come after us?
Tsezguerra: Not right away.
We now have nearly twice
the number of accompany cards
as genthru and his team have.
Rodriot: Yeah, and what if
they use clairvoyant snake?
They’ll find out
what we’re holding.
Tsezguerra: Just watch, genthru.
This is how
a single star hunter fights.
♪
( Gon grunts ) Gyo!
Bisky: Too slow!
Don’t stop to think
after I grab you by the arm.
React as soon
as you feel a touch.
Gon: Osu! ( Yells )
- ( Hand slaps )
- Bisky: Too slow.
Gon: Osu!
- ( Hand slaps )
- Bisky: You’re still too slow!
Gon: Osu!
Bisky: Now let’s take
a ten-minute break
before we start
emitter training.
Gon: Osu!
( Sighs )
Bisky: He’s building up
his stamina,
but in the two weeks
we have left,
I can only help him
bolster his defense.
We need another weapon
before we’re ready to fight.
Emission training, level two--
floating hand.
Hold this stance
by releasing aura,
and stay perfectly still.
See? You’ll pass whenever
you can launch yourself
as high as I just did.
Gon: Okay!
( Grunts )
( Grunting )
Hah!
( Gasps )
( Groans )
Hah!
( Grunting )
Killua: That looks hard.
I mean really hard, considering
that it’s just one level higher.
Bisky: ’course it’s hard.
It’s actually
a level-five exercise.
Killua: Wait. Are you sure it’s
okay to skip levels like that?
Bisky: It’s a gamble.
If it doesn’t work,
the three weeks we’ve been given
will be a waste.
If we followed the proper steps,
he could reach level three
quite easily,
but it wouldn’t do him
very much good in actual combat.
He needs an emitter-type attack
that can push an opponent
back several meters
with a direct hit.
If it’s to be
an effective weapon,
it has to be
at least that strong.
Killua: So that’s
level five, huh?
But even if he does
clear the training,
being able to send your enemies
flying isn’t lethal.
Bisky: That’s exactly right.
The only purpose of training
at this level is to give him
more options to draw on.
So have you come up
with a strategy?
Killua: Yeah, but would you mind
telling me what your ability is?
That’d make it a whole lot
easier to plan it all out.
♪
Bisky: Allow me
to introduce my ability,
cookie, the magical masseuse!
Her various massage techniques
are caresses of pure bliss.
They melt away fat deposits
and leave you feeling heavenly.
Aura is transmuted
into special lotion,
smoothing and
rejuvenating your skin.
Her shiatsu makes you beautiful
from the inside out,
relieving constipation,
stiff muscles, chills,
anything that ails you.
Killua: Uh...
And is that it?
Bisky: No, of course not!
She does chiropractic, Swedish,
and deep tissue massage, too,
and that’s only the beginning!
Killua: What are you, an idiot?!
That crap
is completely worthless!
Bisky: You’re crazy!
It’s obviously the most useful
power in the world!
Killua: You are
such a stupid old hag!
Bisky: I dare you
to say that again!
( Owl hooting )
( Sub gasps )
Barry: Return on! To soufrabi!
Bara: Hey, wait!
Sub: Was it them again?
Bara: The bastards.
Their attacks are getting
pretty damn brazen.
They’re targeting us.
There’s no doubt about it.
Sub: That isn’t the issue here.
The issue is how they always
know right where to find us.
If they used accompany
or magnetic force, we’d know,
but that’s not the case.
They’re using
hit-and-run tactics,
then making clean escapes.
We move
to a different location,
but then there they are
every time.
Genthru: It must be
someone’s ability.
If they aren’t using a spell
for homing or tracking,
the only other explanation
I can come up with
is that one of their members
has a nen ability
that’s similar to radar.
Sub: But we
can’t defend against that!
Bara: What do we do?
Genthru: Hmm.
We’ll just have to resort
to drastic measures.
( Blows striking )
( Body falls )
( Man gasping )
Bara: Nice!
One copy of accompany.
Genthru: All right, then.
Take all his c-rank cards.
( Man gasping )
Bara: Yeah. You got it.
We’ll set peek on his binder.
Sub: So he hasn’t met them.
Bara: It looks like
he’s totally clean.
Genthru: Listen up.
Have you heard of the bombers?
Man: Yes. I’ve heard rumors.
Genthru: We’re the bombers.
( Man yelps )
Genthru:
And I just set a bomb on you.
I can kill you anywhere
and at any time.
If you don’t want to die,
you’ll bring me
all the cards I request.
Bara: Hey, we just scored
another accompany!
Sub: Great.
I’ll set peek in here.
- Bara: Huh?
- ( Genthru groans )
Sub: Damn it! This sucks!
Man #2: Huh?
All: Busted!
( Explosion )
( Birds squawk )
♪
Goreinu: This is bad.
What the hell are
those bastards thinking?
♪
Goreinu: They’re staking out
the spell card shop,
and they’ve been attacking
every player
who walks out
with newly purchased cards.
Now, this is just speculation,
but I think
they might just be aware of me.
They’ve definitely realized
that someone’s been providing
cards to team tsezguerra.
To find me,
they’re checking the binders
of anyone who leaves the shop,
and if they find anyone
who’s met you in person
there’s no discussion.
- They’re killed on the spot.
- ( All gasp )
Goreinu: They’ve also been
stealing all of their cards.
Seems they’re totally focused
on obtaining accompany
and magnetic force.
And any players
who are fully cleared
of suspicion and released
are then forced
to collect cards for them.
By eliminating suspects
and taking their cards,
they’ve effectively
cut off our supply.
They’re killing three birds
with one stone.
Tsezguerra: Understood.
We’ll try and keep track
of their movements from here.
Get away from there now,
and wait for us to contact you.
♪
( Scanner beeping )
Kess: They don’t appear
to be leaving masadora.
Tsezguerra: Okay, so next
we’ll check on their cards.
Rodriot: It looks like
the three of them
have 16 accompanies
and two magnetic forces.
Barry: They’ve gained a lot.
Tsezguerra: At this rate,
they’ll be caught up with us
in just four or five days,
but that’s just about
what we expected.
They don’t plan to move on
until they’re
absolutely positive
that they have enough cards.
12 days left.
We’re right on schedule.
( Gon grunting )
♪
Hah!
( Groans )
I just can’t do it.
Bisky: When training, visualize
yourself firing a water pistol.
Gather your aura. Then shoot it
all out of your palm at once.
The greater the force
you’re able to summon,
the more striking power
the emitted aura will have.
Open up the nodes in your hand,
and emit the aura.
The amount of refined aura
that you apply,
the speed and the power--
oh, yes, and timing--
all of these elements
must be present,
or else you won’t get the effect
you’re looking for.
Gon: It’s too hard!
I get all
the other stuff from before,
but not how you push it
out of your hand.
Killua: He hasn’t
made any progress for ten days.
Maybe you should
have allowed him
to pick it up
from level two after all.
Bisky: We still have
ten more days.
Killua: Yeah, only if
team tsezguerra can deliver.
Looking back on it now, it
wasn’t a very good deal for us.
If we hand over
wild luck alexandrite,
they’re only gonna
be missing two cards.
We still need over 30, and
that’s gonna take us a while.
Bisky: We can just take them
from genthru by force.
It’s not a problem.
Killua: Gon would
never accept that.
Besides, we still have to figure
out how to beat genthru first.
- Bisky: Yes, that’s true.
- ( Gon grunting )
Bisky: So do you think
this is big enough?
Killua: Yeah.
( Birds squawk )
Genthru: We now have
48 copies of accompany.
If you add up
all their accompany, return,
and magnetic force cards,
they only have 45.
- They can’t shake us now.
- ( Both chuckle )
Genthru: So I suggest we start
a game of tag we can’t lose.
Accompany on! Tsezguerra!
♪
Kess: They’re on the way,
and their speed is unbelievable!
Tsezguerra: Stick to the plan!
Tsezguerra:
Accompany on! To masadora!
Genthru:
Accompany on! Tsezguerra!
Tsezguerra: Accompany on!
To soufrabi!
Genthru: Accompany on!
Tsezguerra!
Tsezguerra: Accompany on!
To masadora!
Genthru:
Accompany on! Tsezguerra!
♪
Tsezguerra: I’m all out. Barry!
Barry: Roger.
Accompany on! To soufrabi!
( Gon grunting )
Damn! We’ve only
got five days left!
Killua: Don’t you have
a little bit of advice
that might help him
to break through?
Bisky: The sensation of aura
flowing through the body
is similar,
but different for everyone.
All I can do is try to give him
advice from my own perspective,
but he might make
the wrong assumptions. You know.
( Killua sighs )
Gon: Hah!
Damn it.
Hah!
Tsezguerra: How many left?
Barry: Seven copies
of accompany.
Rodriot: They’re not coming.
You think they gave up?
Tsezguerra: No way.
They’re just taking their time
to throw us off.
Kess: If we run out
of accompany, we have return.
Rodriot: Then we’ll alternate
between aiai and soufrabi.
Barry: How is it over there?
Tsezguerra: Let’s find out.
And contact on. Goreinu.
It’s tsezguerra. How’s it going?
Goreinu: Looks like
you were right.
Sub and bara showed up,
most likely the real ones.
They might be speculating
that i’ll try to buy cards
while they’re off playing tag.
That means that the ones
who are chasing you
are genthru
and a couple of fakes.
Rodriot: It sounds like
your predictions
were pretty accurate.
Tsezguerra: That same trick
won’t work again.
Kess: There are four of us,
and genthru’s all by himself.
If you ask me, now’s our chance.
Tsezguerra: Not yet.
I’d prefer much better odds
before we fight them.
We’ll stick to the plan.
( Spell whooshing )
Here they come. We’re back on!
- Gon: Hah!
- ( Aura whooshes )
( Gasping )
Killua: Gon.
Your time’s up.
Training’s over.
Gon: But we still
have five days!
Killua: Had a change in plans.
We’ve formed a new strategy
to defeat them.
Gon: Yeah, but hold on.
See, the thing is
I think i’m getting
really close, maybe.
Killua: Not happening.
I can’t base our whole strategy
on a new technique
that isn’t reliable yet.
- Just give up.
- ( Gon groans )
Killua: Okay. So the plan is--
bisky: To use this card.
Gon: Eh?
Killua: You’ll have to learn it
the hard way.
Practice ’til you’ve
got it perfect.
Gon: Uh...
( Spell whooshing )
Barry: We’re out of accompanies.
Tsezguerra: Use return.
All: Return on! To aiai!
Genthru: They’re out
of accompanies, are they?
Endgame’s almost upon us.
Sub, bara,
have you caught anyone?
Sub: Yeah, but just one.
And it was a newbie,
so he was pretty inexperienced.
Word got out that the bombers
are hunting players,
so everyone’s staying clear.
Well, what do you think?
Could he have been
someone we’ve already killed?
Genthru: Perhaps.
All right, just come back
when you’re ready.
I’m in soufrabi right now.
( Fakes whimper )
Genthru: It seems they’ve
run out of ammunition.
♪
Tsezguerra:
We’re on our last card.
If they try to follow us
outside the game,
we can just hole up
at the mansion.
Rodriot: And if
they don’t follow us,
we just have
to run out the clock.
Kess: This is perfect.
Let’s pick the cards
we’ll keep once we win.
Barry: Before we do,
we should ask Mr. Battera
which ones he wants.
( Spell whooshing )
Tsezguerra: All right! Let’s go!
Leave on!
Rodriot: Nobody’s in here.
Kess: Wait. What’s going on?
There were supposed
to be armed guards.
Tsezguerra: Where are you?
Speak up! Hey, sabazushi!
Answer me!
Sabazushi: Keep it down.
Some of us were trying
to catch a nap here.
Tsezguerra: You were sleeping?
What the hell
happened to everyone else?
- Sabazushi: Oh, they all left.
- Tsezguerra: Huh?
Sabazushi: Mr. Battera
scrapped the whole thing.
We received a cancellation fee
and an intermediary fee,
but I stuck around
to let you know.
Tsezguerra: It was canceled?
Mr. Battera,
what is the meaning of this?!
We’ve come so far.
We’ve almost beaten the game!
Battera: It doesn’t matter,
not anymore.
( Tsezguerra groans )
"Doesn’t matter"? What is that?!
What about all the time
and effort we spent?!
Battera: My lawyers have been
instructed to pay you.
As for the cards,
do with them as you wish.
So now, please,
I just want to be left alone,
I beg you.
( Tsezguerra groans )
Damn it!
Kess: You find out
what’s happening?
Tsezguerra: No idea,
but i’m determined to find out.
- ( Explosion )
- ( Sabazushi screams )
( Gurgles )
Genthru: We can kill
all we want out here,
since we won’t lose
any ring data.
( Chuckles )
Narrator: Team tsezguerra
his given gon and his friends
the time they’d promised,
but waiting for them
was a situation
they did not expect.
♪
( Singing in Japanese )