Bopobo:
Who the hell are you guys?
Look, this is a private party.
So get lost!
We’re only here to talk.
Would you please leave
this town?
( All laughing )
been a long time
since we heard that line.
( Laughter continues )
Man: ( Singing in Japanese )
♪
( Laughter )
( Laughter continues )
( Glass clinking )
If you want us to leave here,
talking
just ain’t gonna cut it.
♪
I don’t care how many of you
attack me at once.
If you can knock me
out of this ring,
then i’ll take you guys over
to see our boss.
wait, knock you out
of the ring? Is that all?
if it’s brawn
you’re looking for,
then i’m your man!
( Roaring )
Killua: ( Thinking )
what a joke.
That long to produce
so little ren?
( Growling )
( Straining )
( Groans )
I’ll admit.
You’re stronger than I thought.
( Chuckling )
( Straining )
( Yelling )
let me go!
I give up! I lose!
Just let me go!
( Groans )
( Panting )
Gon: He said he lost already.
Why didn’t you let him go?
He knew what the rules are.
You lose if you step
outside the ring.
Anything else,
including a forfeit,
is completely meaningless.
You kicked me,
then stepped outside
the ring too.
So you lost as well.
( Groans )
oh, no.
Hold on a second.
Let’s start over.
Don’t bother, gon.
You’re probably eager to try out
your big ultimate move,
but hold off.
not in front
of all these people.
Here, i’ll handle it.
What’s this?
Are you gonna team up on me?
Let me borrow this.
Huh?
( Glass clinks )
You wouldn’t!
( Whooshing )
( Gurgles )
( Electricity crackling )
( Yelling )
( Both gasp )
( Straining )
( Yelling )
( Rumbling thud )
( All gasp )
Well. Guess I win.
( Panting )
( Growling )
You brat.
You’re dead!
( Groans )
( All gasp )
( Grunts )
you made up
all of the rules yourself.
So get over it.
Yeah, that’s on me.
This way.
I’ll take you to the boss.
♪
( Both gasp )
killua:
This is where your boss is?
♪
pirate 68-b:
Got visitors, boss.
Razor:
Yeah, and who are they?
pirate 68-b: Seems
they want us to leave town.
Razor: That so?
( Chuckles )
( Grunts )
Then let’s have a contest,
shall we?
If you win,
we’ll leave the island
peacefully.
It’ll be up to us to choose
what the contest will be.
All right?
And what if we lose?
What’ll happen to us then?
Oh, nothing really.
You’ll just have
to leave instead.
Simple as that.
Fine. Let’s go.
It’s an athletics contest.
where each member
will challenge you to a match
in their specialty sport.
One win each.
First to eight wins
is the Victor.
My challenge is first up,
and i’m gonna go with boxing.
Well, who wants to take him?
I’ve got this one.
Razor: There is just one
special condition.
You can use items
conjured by nen.
What the hell?
You can’t call that boxing!
Don’t worry about it.
I’m just gonna use my fists.
That rule is only
for your benefit.
Tag out if you want to.
That’s not gonna happen.
Fight!
( Bell dings )
♪
I know what’s going on here.
But I figure
if you choose boxing,
there must be a reason.
♪
You’re an emitter too,
aren’t ya?
We’re fighting
in close proximity,
and this--
well, this is a finite space.
Making it an ideal situation
for an emitter.
But you made one mistake.
Not anticipating
that I might be
stronger than you!
Wow! He can’t dodge that speed!
( Grunting )
( Yells )
( Groaning )
Yes, he’s down!
That was easy.
No, they were both hit.
( Gasps )
( All gasping )
( Thuds )
( Groans )
What in the hell just happened?
How?
( Thinking ) These guys
really didn’t see that?
Their guy teleported.
Wait, what do you mean?
Just his fist.
A short uppercut.
( Whooshing )
killua:
From the very start,
his goal was to land
a knockout counter.
( Whooshing )
i thought
it was pretty obvious.
( Chuckles )
Seems he’s out cold.
That looks like a win
for our side.
Damn.
( Sighs )
( Thinking )
Eight wins with them
will be impossible.
Which means...
Now, for the next challenge,
we’re juggling soccer balls.
Okay, i’m up.
Wait a minute.
Huh?
Hmm?
All right.
That would be
quite wise indeed.
Hmm.
Hi, this round is you and me.
A little girl, huh?
I guess i’ll have to be
real careful not to injure you.
Injure me with juggling?
Hmm.
We’re both allowed to attack
using our nen,
if you don’t touch the ball
with your hands.
Yes, I get it.
Moving is allowed
anywhere inside the building.
And whoever
drops the ball first loses.
right.
I understand.
Okay.
Then let’s get started.
Ready?
Go!
♪
( All gasping )
Oh, goodness.
That was much harder
than I expected.
I guess I lose.
I’m next, big guy.
Do you wanna go?
Yeah, you think?
You are so gonna get it!
Razor:
Ready? And fight!
I’ll squash you like a bug!
( Grunts )
♪
Oh, sorry.
I stepped outside the ring.
( Thinking )
okay.
i think I see
what they’re up to.
♪
( Whistle blowing )
razor:
That’s eight wins for us.
So we’re the Victors.
pirate 68-b:
Go on, get out of here.
We’ll keep doing whatever
we want in this town.
Where are you going,
you little snot?
Fight me again!
♪
You knew we couldn’t win
with this lineup.
So you threw it
and totally focused
on gathering information.
but once a party
has been defeated,
there are no second chances.
It’s all right.
We just need
to switch out one member.
So it was well worth the risk.
Asta: Our team’s dropping out.
( All gasping )
We fulfilled
our original objective--
preventing the bomber
from winning the game.
It’ll be impossible for them
to assemble a group
of 15 players.
you should give up
on this contest for a bit.
Asta: If you do get the card,
you’ll just become targets.
♪
( Energy whooshing )
goreinu:
Those guys just don’t get it.
Our strategy...
it makes sense to obtain
this card as fast as we can.
right.
In order to reduce
the chances of fighting
within the group.
Exactly.
( Gasps )
Killua: You need at least
15 people to participate.
Even if you use clone,
you can only obtain three copies
of "strip of beach."
Looks to me like this event
was specially designed
to incite infighting.
( Both gasping )
That’s what you were talking
about before, wasn’t it?
Whoa, that’s pretty brutal.
Of course.
I didn’t understand it
right away.
Assuming that the 4 of us
are capable of winning,
we need 4 more with us
who are up to the task.
In a perfect world,
they would already be
in a group of 11.
Do you have any leads?
Now book.
gon:
Going by the names on my list,
it looks like chrollo’s
probably the strongest.
but kurapika told me
that the chrollo here
is definitely an impostor.
So who do you think
it is, then?
well, probably
a member of the troupe.
Gon: But why would a member
of the troupe be here?
killua: Not sure.
Maybe to beat the game?
Well, then why wouldn’t they
want to use their own name?
I have no idea.
goreinu:
Try using clairvoyance.
( All gasping )
if this person
didn’t come all the way here
to beat the game,
they simply wouldn’t bother
collecting cards.
Gon: Yeah, you’re right.
killua: Wow.
This guy isn’t even trying.
Looks like
the only cards he’s obtained
are for food and water.
actually, that can make it
a lot easier to invite them.
but if it really is
a member of the troupe,
we won’t invite them.
We’ll see what they say.
Yeah? Well, then what’s
the point of even trying?
We already know
it’s one of them.
We need to know who they are,
but why they’re here
is more important.
What are you, a damn idiot?
are you just gonna
ask them why they’re here?
Because, big surprise,
they’re not gonna tell you!
Yeah, i’m an idiot, fine.
But i’m still gonna ask,
and you can’t stop me.
Then go right ahead!
Great, maybe I will!
Are they okay?
This kind of thing
happens every day.
Gon: I’m going.
Then quit yapping
and just do it.
( Both growling )
( Sighs )
Gon: Accompany on!
Chrollo lucilfer!
( Energy whooshing )
( Water sloshing )
( Sloshing continues )
( All gasp )
No way.
Gon: Hisoka!
Hmm?
( Gasps )
What have we here?
it seems I have
unexpected guests.
Long time no see.
( Whooshing )
( Both whooshing )
( Sinister chuckling )
Just as I suspected.
You’ve matured quite a lot,
haven’t you?
You’ve clearly found
an excellent teacher.
You’ll continue to ripen
into sweet fruit,
just as I thought.
Uh, okay.
So do you guys actually
know this pervert?
Ahh.
You must be their teacher,
I assume. No.
Doesn’t seem the type.
( Yells )
Oh, no! Oh, my gosh!
It’s her?
What do you want with me?
Or perhaps more accurately,
with chrollo?
Gon: I have a question.
What are you doing in the game?
( Thinking )
Well, what to do now?
if I talk,
I know how they’ll react.
They’ll do everything
in their power
to keep the spiders
from the nen exorcist.
That could be interesting
in and of itself,
but I don’t want to delay
my fight with chrollo
any longer than I have to.
I came here
to look for chrollo.
( Both gasping )
He’s still crippled
by kurapika’s nen,
but there’s actually
a way to remove it.
Gon: Exorcism.
Hisoka: You knew?
well, that will
make this much easier.
I’m looking for chrollo
to pass that along,
but I have no leads.
Before long,
i remembered
that some of the spiders
were interested in this game.
so, of course,
if I can locate them,
they might be able to tell me
where chrollo is.
And using his handle
all but guarantees
they’ll try to contact me.
Okay.
So he was just pretending
to be a member
of the phantom troupe.
Yeah.
Now I have a question for you.
Tell me.
Did the two of you really
come all the way out here
just to ask me that?
Yeah. Sure did.
( Sighs )
Um...
The truth is,
we’re here looking for people
who are really strong,
and we were hoping
you might join us.
( Both groaning )
huh?
All right.
May I ask why you’re looking
for strong people?
hey, wait a minute.
I don’t think I like this.
It’s risky.
It sure is!
you don’t know
who this guys is, bisky!
what? Of course
I know who he is.
( Both gasp )
Not personally,
but I feel
a certain kinship with him.
the city of love, aiai,
isn’t very far from here.
you can meet
all kinds of people.
You might even find the strength
that you’re looking for.
♪
What exactly did you mean
about him lying?
Well, technically,
I should’ve said that
he wasn’t telling the truth.
But how could you tell?
It was really more of a hunch.
Seriously?
After lying
for 50 years myself,
I can recognize a fellow liar.
( Laughing )
that’s...
Actually pretty convincing.
Biscuit: It’s obvious
he’s hiding something.
So best to keep him around
until we can find out what.
Plus, he’s really strong,
isn’t he?
Gon: Yeah...
♪
( Both straining )
Killua: Hey, hisoka!
You walk in front!
Ten more members.
That’s what we need, correct?
yeah.
Members like you.
people who have little
or no interest in cards.
I would’ve thought everyone else
was here to beat the game.
I doubt there are many other
eccentrics like myself.
( Thinking )
Oh, he’s hiding something.
I can feel it.
( Fawning )
By the way,
did you use someone’s power
to fly over here by any chance?
it’s a spell.
The game is full of ’em.
Oh, so that’s what it was.
You’ll need to buy spells
from stores, yes?
( Thinking )
Something doesn’t make sense.
If he isn’t being honest
with us,
there must be some kind
of inconsistency in his words.
He says he only came here
to find spiders
who might know
where to find chrollo.
There’s gotta be a clue
in there somewhere.
( Distant chanting )
Aiai, aiai, aiai...
( Shrieks )
oh, no!
Where are my glasses?
Hisoka: Get them for her.
You might become friends.
( Girl grunts )
Excuse me!
you should watch
where you’re going!
Be more careful!
Uh, sorry.
( Grunts )
Now i’m gonna be late!
Why did you apologize?
What you should have done
is told her to watch
where she was going,
starting an argument.
Girl: Stop it! Please!
let me go!
I swear i’ll scream!
Fine, scream your heart out.
Not like anybody’s
gonna save you.
Gon: Hold it right there!
You let her go right now!
( Grunts )
Hey, that hurt.
What are you doing falling for
such a tired old cliche, huh?
Biscuit: Really?
you want me
to be your hair model?
Your hair’s so long
and lovely.
It would be my honor
to style it.
Yes!
There’s no point in us
hanging around
this stupid city.
hisoka,
let’s go somewhere else.
But why?
at least here,
boredom isn’t an issue.
( Thinking )
boredom?
That’s it.
That’s what didn’t click
earlier.
it’s this place
that’s the problem.
if I entered this game
just to hunt someone down,
what would I do?
First, i’d see how important
the spell cards are.
Gon and bisky ran into hisoka
while I was outside
retaking the hunter exam.
That must have been while they
were training near masadora.
He was in masadora!
Normally it wouldn’t make sense
for him to leave.
Most players pass through there
looking for spell cards.
If he really was looking
for the troupe,
he wouldn’t have left.
( Thinking ) At least here,
boredom isn’t an issue.
( Thinking )
He’s bored because
he’s got nothing to do.
So he isn’t looking for anyone.
No! He’s already found them.
That’s it.
That’s in line with what bisky
was saying earlier.
Hisoka already met up
with the troupe.
Now he’s waiting
for something.
But what?
What else could--
an exorcist!
The exorcist is here
on greed island.
Hisoka and the troupe
already know that.
I can’t tell gon about it yet.
He’s a terrible liar.
If hisoka finds out we know,
he’s bound to slip away
from us.
if he leaves,
we’ll be down an ally
and we won’t know
what the troupe is doing.
We can’t let that happen.
gon: Hey, killua?
I’ve been thinking.
Tsezguerra.
we should probably
try to recruit him.
even if he won’t join,
we should at least meet him.
And that way, he’ll be on
our binder list.
Yeah, it’d be better if we knew
what they were up to.
( Gasps )
( Thinking ) The binder!
We can find out for sure.
Can I see your binder,
hisoka?
We’re trying to find a guy
named tsezguerra,
so I want to see
if he’s on the list
of players you’ve met.
List?
( Thinking )
This is perfect.
if I started asking
a bunch of questions,
hisoka would get suspicious.
But since gon
doesn’t know anything,
hisoka won’t see
a problem with it.
Book.
Killua: ( Thinking )
If he refuses
to show us the screen,
that’ll just support
my theory.
Hisoka: There he is.
tsezguerra.
Really?
Yes. Look. Here
( thinking )
He’s showing us? No way!
It doesn’t look
like there are
any troupe members listed.
Was I being paranoid?
could hisoka actually
still be looking for them?
Hmm.
in that case,
would you recite this spell?
Don’t worry.
We’ll do all the talking.
Hisoka: Contact on.
tsezguerra.
( Energy whooshes )
( Chuckling )
My texture surprise certainly
does come in handy.
Man: ( Singing in Japanese )
Narrator: Hisoka’s ability
completely fools
killua and his friends.
But the question remains,
is he friend or foe?
♪