Killua: Yeah! All right!
We made it!
Gon: Yeah, we did!
That was great!
We must have gone
five kilometers today!
Killua: When we
first got started,
I thought it’d take years,
but at this pace...
Hello, masadora!
Gon: For the second time!
Bisky: Okay! Now let’s head
right back to where we were.
Both: Again?!
♪
( Singing in Japanese )
Bisky: Next we’re going to work
on collecting monster cards.
You now have
the physical strength
to beat every enemy
you might encounter here,
but what you lack is strategy,
the ability to think
while you’re on your feet,
and that’s important whenever
you’re fighting an enemy,
so combat analysis skills.
Gon: Wait. Combat...
Killua: Analysis skills?
Bisky: Now, I won’t be
handing out advice freely,
so you’ll have
to try and figure out
your own methods
for defeating the monsters.
( Monster squeals )
Still, all things considered,
the game’s creators
were actually pretty smart.
It’s programmed so that
the player is guaranteed
to get stronger
as they progress.
And most likely,
it’s all for the purpose
of making that child stronger.
( Monster squeals )
Gon: I did it!
I got the hyper puffball!
( Monster growls )
Bisky: One must battle
a wide variety of enemies
in nen combat.
The most critical
of all of the battle skills
is the ability to think quickly.
You have to get used
to thinking constantly
until your thoughts
are tied to your reflexes.
This game is a training regimen
to help you achieve that.
The hardest monster to defeat in
this area is the bubble horse.
Once they clear that,
they’ll have completed
the second phase.
♪
Gon: Zetsu!
( Bubble horse neighs )
I got ya!
Bubble horse! I got one!
- Killua: Way to go, gon.
- Gon: Thanks!
Bisky: When it comes to analysis
and physical strength,
killua has the edge,
but gon makes up for it
with his concentration
and lightning-fast
recovery speed.
Those two really make
a perfect team.
Okay. Now we’ll begin
training you in defense.
♪
Gon: Hey, is that--
bisky: That’s right, gon.
This is the technique
you’ve both been using.
Ten, zetsu, ren, hatsu, and gyo
are all combined in this
single technique called ko.
You focus every ounce
of your aura
into one part of your body
and then attack.
This method gives it
far greater power
than your regular attacks
ever could.
I’m going to attack you
with my fist,
and you must block my attacks
by any means necessary.
No dodging allowed.
( Both gasp )
Bisky: Figured it out yet?
That’s right.
If you use your aura
to block normally,
you’ll take
considerable damage.
So instead?
Gon: We should use ko as well.
Bisky: You’re half right.
Ko versus ko.
Unless the disparity in power
is too great,
a well-executed block
will protect you, but...
If your opponent
hits you in a place
where you weren’t using ko,
you’ll be destroyed.
Killua: Then we should use ko
on our entire body,
but it sounds contradictory.
Bisky: Exactly. This technique
combines both ten and ren.
It’s known as Ken.
You defend yourself
by shrouding your body
in much more aura than usual.
It isn’t as strong as ko,
of course,
but it’s
infinitely more practical.
Gon. Use ren, please.
Ken is sustaining that
for a long time.
Now protect yourself
from my punch, if you can.
♪
Gon: Eh?
It’s so slow.
( Killua gasps )
Bisky: You let your guard down
when you saw
how slowly I was moving.
If you’d stopped using Ken,
I would have crushed your face.
That’s the power of ko
by itself.
When I add the speed and power
packed into a normal punch,
it gets stronger,
many times stronger,
as a matter of fact,
perhaps even dozens.
( Gon grunts )
Bisky: I’ll start
by going slowly,
and don’t expect a warning.
Keep using Ken,
and try your best
to withstand my attacks.
( Gon gasping )
Killua: Gon!
Bisky: Hmm. That was
almost a full two minutes.
Gon: I had no idea
that trying to maintain my ren
for so long would be so hard!
Bisky: If you want
to stand a chance,
you’ll need to be able
to sustain Ken
for at least 30 minutes.
( Both grunting )
Killua: All right! We’re done!
Gon: Time to practice Ken!
( Grunting )
( Blow strikes )
( Gasping )
Bisky: Good! That’s 30 minutes.
You’ve certainly gotten a lot
tougher over the past month.
Both: The number three!
Bisky: Ding! Killua by a hair.
Gon, give me
a thousand push-ups.
( Gon grunting )
Bisky: All right,
today, we’ll begin
actual combat training.
Ken!
♪
In your current state,
both your attack power
and your defense are at 50,
which means that, at this point,
if you were to fight
each other using Ken,
you wouldn’t be able
to cause much damage at all.
So what do you do?
Gon: We use our ko!
Bisky: No, you dummy!
What if he hits you
where you’re not using ko?
What then?
Killua: We use gyo?
Bisky: Correct!
So with an even split
right at the moment of attack,
shift offensive and defensive
power of your right fist to 70
and the rest of it to 30,
and then you can use gyo
to change the ratio of power
to suit your situation.
This is called ryu!
Now set your right hand to 70
for offense and defense
and the rest to 30.
It doesn’t have to be precise.
Just try it out.
( Both grunting )
Bisky: Left foot to 80,
your body to 20.
Now head to 60,
your body to 40!
( Both panting )
Bisky: Do this for 30 minutes
three times a day
along with your current
training regimen.
Also...
We’ll begin sparring.
Use ryu just as I taught you.
Start out by trying it slowly.
When you’re on the defensive,
you’ll want to determine
your opponent’s attack power
before defending with ryu.
With that said, begin!
Killua: I’ll go first,
okay, gon?
Right foot, 55 on both fronts.
Gon: Right foot, 60 offensive
and defensive, I think.
Left hand, 60 for both.
♪
Right fist,
80 offensive and defensive.
Left elbow, 80 offensive
and defensive power.
Bisky: If they keep this up
every day for two months,
they should be able
to fight easily at full speed
while still using ryu.
And then the final phase begins.
♪
( Gon and killua grunting )
Bisky: Okay! Break time!
Both: Thank you
for sparring with me.
Osu!
Bisky: It’s been two weeks.
You’ve made a lot of progress.
It looks like you’re both ready
to enter
the final phase of training.
Both: Final phase, huh?
Bisky: Yes.
You’ll start training
in individual categories.
Both: Three!
Bisky: Bingo!
That was a tie.
You can train exclusively
in your own category.
In the case of an enhancer...
You’ll focus
on your enhancer skills
while training in transmuter
and emitter abilities equally.
That’ll help you master
your own category faster.
( Aura pops )
Both: Nine!
Bisky: Well done.
Another tie.
Gon: Really good job, killua.
Killua: Yeah, same to you.
Bisky: Now let’s get started.
Both: Osu!
Bisky: We’ll start off
in the enhancer category.
The first exercise
is breaking rocks.
And I want you
to break them like this.
Smash a thousand
with a single stone in a day,
and you’ll clear the level.
Now begin!
( Both grunting )
Killua: This is pretty tough.
I’m just changing the stone’s
offensive and defensive power
to 100
right at the moment of impact,
but I can feel my nen
getting weaker as I go.
( Gon gasps )
Aw, it crumbled!
Bisky: If the stone
in your hand breaks, it’s over.
( Gon groans )
( Killua gasps )
Damn it! I messed it up!
Bisky: What are
you talking about?
You were actually doing well.
Killua: Okay,
let’s do
a transmuter exercise next!
Bisky: Now, now.
Don’t be so hasty.
You’re only allowed to train
in one category per day.
- Gon: A six!
- Killua: Six!
Bisky: Right! Tied again!
Killua: Really?
Gon: We keep tying.
Bisky: All that means
is that you’re both growing
a lot more accustomed
to using gyo.
Killua: But it’s not any fun
if there’s no winner.
Gon: Then let’s decide
with rock-paper-scissors,
and the loser has to do
a thousand push-ups, okay?
Killua: Fine by me.
Both: Now show me rock!
Jan Ken pon!
Gon: I win!
Killua: Damn it!
Bisky: Hey, boys, have you heard
that this game
is based on the martial arts?
Killua: Uh...
Bisky: Paper represents
a palm attack to the organs.
Scissors represent
a finger jab to the vitals.
Rock represents a punch
targeting muscle and bone.
A long time ago, martial arts
were called jaken, or evil fist,
and considered so destructive
that they were
completely forbidden.
But masters were able
to continue their training
by pretending to play.
And that’s how
many people think janken,
or rock-paper-scissors,
first came to be.
Killua: Wow...
You’re really old.
( Bisky yells )
Gon: That’s it, the jaken.
( Bisky groans ) Huh?
Gon: Evil fist.
( Birds squawk )
Player: Gentlemen,
we currently have
133 specified-slot cards
of 90 different types,
and of course it’s all thanks
to your tireless efforts.
Of the remaining 10 cards,
we know the location
of seven of them.
They’ll be ours
before you know it.
But tsezgerra’s group
is closing in.
They’ve obtained the same number
of specified-slot cards,
and now the final hurdle
will likely be a showdown
against their group.
However, I believe
we have more spell cards
and of much higher quality,
so our victory
is all but assured.
( Players cheering )
Player #2: May I?
I have something to say.
Player #1: Hmm?
Player #2: These past five years
have been so long,
yet so fleeting.
And now there’s something
that I feel I really need
to share with you.
I am the bomber.
( Players gasping, murmuring )
Player #3: What? The bomber?
Player #1: Hey, wait.
What are you talking about?
Bomber: Please, hear me out.
I’ve already planted bombs
on each and every one of you.
- ( Players gasping )
- Player #4: You what?!
Player #5: How did
you even do that?
Player #6: Yeah!
You’re kidding, right?
Bomber: Calm down, and listen.
( Player #7 groans )
Bomber: Oh, dear.
You’ve disrupted
the proper sequence
of my explanation.
This is my ability,
little flower.
You see, I can blow up
anything that I grab,
but it isn’t all that strong.
He’s still alive, of course.
However, if the bombs
on your bodies
were to suddenly explode,
you would die.
♪
( Players murmuring )
Player #8: A bomb?
But where is it?
Bomber: Listen up,
and i’ll be more than happy
to tell you how to disarm them.
Let’s begin with how I set them.
That was simply by touching
the place on the target
I wished to explode
and uttering a certain keyword,
which is...
"Bomber."
( Players gasp )
Bomber: It sounds like
it was the bomber.
Listen. Beware of the bomber.
To disarm the bombs,
you must touch me
somewhere on my body
and then say the phrase,
"I caught the bomber."
That said, don’t forget
about my secret weapon,
the little flower ability.
I can use it to stop
anyone who tries to touch me.
You must be very careful when
attempting to disarm the bombs.
That’s all.
( Bombs ticking )
( Players gasping )
Player #9: They’re armed!
Bomber: What’s the matter now?
My other ability is countdown.
Why am I telling you
all of this,
you might be wondering.
That’s the condition for arming
the bombs I planted on you.
Player #10: Then you were
just waiting for the day
that all of the cards
and members were gathered.
Bomber: And now
I have a proposition.
I will trade your lives
for the 90 specified-slot cards
you’ve obtained.
If you agree to my terms, then I
will use an alternative method
to simultaneously disarm
all of the bombs.
Do nothing,
and all of you will die
when the counter reaches zero.
You should discuss this
amongst yourselves.
I’ll be waiting for you
at Mr. Battera’s old mansion,
and whoever comes
must come alone.
Puhat: Do you have a screw loose
or something, buddy?
If we just catch you right here
and now and disarm the bombs,
it’s all over.
Player #1: It’s you against us.
Do you really think
we’ll just let you walk away?
Bomber: Relax.
If you get too excited,
the countdown will accelerate.
I should have mentioned
that the counter
is linked to your heartbeat.
Player #1: What?
- ( Players gasping )
- Bomber: Book!
Player #1: No!
( Bomber laughs )
I do hope that we
meet again soon!
Leave on!
Player #11:
He escaped out of the game!
Player #12: Hurry!
We gotta follow him!
Player #13: Wait.
But if we leave,
the spell cards in our binders
will vanish!
Player #14: So what do we do?!
Player #15: Just calm down!
Going after that guy
would be foolish!
Did you already forget
why we decided to team up
in the first place?
Because none of us
are strong enough fighters!
Does anyone here actually think
we’re powerful enough
to beat him?
Player #10: It’s impossible.
He must be quite strong.
His nen abilities prove it.
If all of us decided to attack
him together as a unified front,
he could simply use
little flower to stop us.
Player #16: Damn!
We were getting so close, too.
Player #10: To start,
it’s imperative
that we come to a consensus.
Do we try to fight, or do we
just hand over the cards?
Player #1:
Hand them over, please!
Do it.
I’m sorry, but jispa
is running out of time.
Bomber: What a surprise.
I had assumed that nickes
would be the one to show up.
Puhat: I’m surprised, too.
Thought you’d have
had company. ( Gasps )
Bomber: Sub and bara.
They’re the other bombers.
Now i’ll have to ask you
to hand over your ring.
( Puhat sighs )
Bomber: What’s wrong?
Puhat: I can’t turn it over yet.
Thing is,
we still haven’t agreed,
and nickes has a request.
He wants you to let us have
the angel’s breath card
so that we can use it
to save jispa.
Bomber: I refuse!
Puhat: As it stands,
neither side can win!
You don’t realize how hysterical
they’re all being right now.
If they can’t decide in time
and they explode,
then you lose everything,
all the data in their rings.
You need me.
Bomber: You can convince them?
- Is that what you’re saying?
- ( Puhat gags )
Are you really trying
to bargain with me?
Because when you
sit down to negotiate,
you have to demonstrate
to your opponent
just how calm
and insane you are.
Puhat: Hey! Wait!
If you kill me now--
( explosion )
( Body thuds )
Bomber: Don’t worry.
If you kill a player outside
the game and take their ring,
their specified slots’
card data remains intact.
Well, someone has the cards,
but I highly doubt
that it’s you.
♪
Both: Hmm?
Bara: I brought you a gift.
( Players gasp )
Player #17: Puhat!
Bara: You won’t get
another chance. Got it?
Leave.
Hand over the leave card
right now.
I need to go, so hurry.
Player #16: You’re crazy!
Leave is a really valuable card,
and we can’t waste any!
Bara: All right,
have it your way,
but if I don’t come back here,
you can’t disarm all
of your bombs simultaneously.
Player #16: What?
Bara: Well,
i’m also a bomber. So...
( Players gasp )
Bara: There are three of us.
Well, genthru’s the main one.
The rest of us
are basically his wingmen.
When the three of us
join our right thumbs
and say the keyword,
the bombs will be destroyed,
and that is
the alternative method.
Whatever.
I’ll take my time returning
by traditional means,
and you’ll all be dead soon.
Player #15: Wait!
Hold on a minute!
Here. You can just take it.
Bara: Should have done that
in the first place!
We’ll need leave cards
when the deal is made,
so get three of ’em ready.
Got that?
Narrator:
A mere 12 hours earlier,
genthru revealed himself
as the infamous bomber,
and a single boat
attempted to invade
the island from the outside.
Shalnark: So it does exist
in the real world.
This must be it, greed island.
♪
( Singing in Japanese )