( Wind blowing )
♪
Narrator: The king transformed
his en into countless photons,
and then
he scattered them everywhere.
Meruem: If there
are any conditions
for komugi’s safe return, speak.
♪
It seems to me that there
is only one person here,
but I shall address you
in the plural.
Palm: He knows
exactly what we’re doing.
Why try to fool him?
Meruem: What I felt
when sensing your en
was not wrath or fear or hate.
Instead, I felt
duty and resolve,
both of which surprised me.
If it is humanity’s survival
that you are fighting for,
then fight no more.
( Palm gasps )
Meruem: Shall I explain further?
It seems you doubt
what you’ve just heard,
so i’ll say it again.
You are victorious.
The battle is over.
I will speak to you now
as an individual.
( Palm gasps )
Meruem: I am here
for a simple reason.
I have but one motive.
The human girl named komugi,
we must speak.
( Palm gasps )
Meruem: In truth,
that is all I want.
There is truly nothing else
which I desire.
I felt your nen, and I believe
you have some insight
into my current condition.
Even knowing what will happen,
I have but one great desire,
and that is to spend
my remaining time with komugi
and nothing more.
( Door creaks )
♪
Palm: Is this a ploy,
a strategy devised
to exploit my psychology?
No, it’s not. It’s impossible.
You expect me to believe you?!
Seriously?!
You think i’ll accept that?!
An omnipotent king
would never lie to himself
in order to fool
someone as lowly as me.
After all the killing
that you’ve done
and that you plan to do,
a creature such as you...
The king admits defeat?
He cares for a human?
No! It doesn’t make sense!
He’s doing this,
because it’s the truth.
Meruem: I believe that it
was only a minimal change.
Palm: Huh?
Meruem: Something
somewhere shifted.
If only I had been this way
from the beginning...
While I am no god,
what is it that I could do
with this world?
No. There is
really only one reason
that I would feel as I do,
because now
everything’s fallen into place.
You know that I have
precious little time left.
I wanted to ask you
instead of searching myself.
Palm: What are you saying?!
( Thinking )
Stop this.
You’re right.
I know exactly where komugi is,
but why don’t you
just torture it out of me?
( Thinking )
I know why.
Meruem: I don’t think
I have to tell you
that that is not
a viable option now.
Your aura is strong
and as starkly beautiful
as any I have ever seen.
Palm: Stop it.
Meruem: All that I can do now is
to ask you for your assistance.
♪
Palm: No, don’t!
A part of me
is a chimera ant now.
I know what you mean
to us as a species,
as much as I hate it.
He loves her that much...
To go to such lengths.
Anything but that.
I’ll tell you.
But on one condition.
May I use my ability to watch,
to see your final moments
with her?
Meruem: If that
is what you require,
then you have my permission.
♪
Palm: Killua, i’m sorry.
I wanted to,
but I couldn’t keep our promise.
( Wind blowing )
( Fabric fluttering )
( Creaking, scraping )
( Komugi breathing heavily )
Four-seven-one, king.
( Murmurs )
( Meruem chuckles )
Wake up, komugi. Let’s play.
( Rotors whirring )
Reporter: We have
a shocking breaking news update.
The reason that
the dictator of east gorteau
assembled the entire country
in one place for a rally
has been revealed
by our sources to be genocide.
Diego’s body
was found under the rubble,
increasing speculation that this
was a planned murder-suicide
on a national level.
It’s been reported
that the whereabouts of bizeff,
diego’s second-in-command
are currently unknown.
We have spoken
to several informed sources,
who say this could have been
a military takeover.
Meanwhile,
the situation in the ngl
and other countries
in the mitene union
is also unsettling.
Inquiries, including requests
to confirm refugees,
have so far been met
with complete silence.
As you know,
dark rumors have long swirled
around east gorteau and the ngl.
This incident may provide
the perfect opportunity
for the international community
to conduct an investigation
morel: Huh? Yeah.
Well, the boss did his job,
that’s for sure.
No. I wasn’t there
to see it go down.
Sorry.
It’s too complicated to explain.
Anyway, we’re waiting on palm.
Beans: Are you sure?
Relying on only one person
to verify the king’s death?
And correct me if i’m wrong,
but she was absorbed
by the enemy, right?
Morel: Well, if you don’t want
to take her word for it,
i’m sure one of
your pencil pushers would write
a perfect follow-up report
if you really wanted.
I know how you guys are,
sitting at your comfortable desk
in your air-conditioned rooms.
It’s different
out here in the field.
When an ally says they’ll
handle it, you trust ’em.
We’re all professionals,
but i’m on the ground here!
You got that?!
( Beans sighs )
I’m afraid that logic
simply won’t fly
with the vice-chair camp,
and if they find out,
you will be
subject to a hearing.
( Typing )
Netero: Uh, my name is netero.
( Beans shuddering )
Thank you for a job
well done, chairman.
Rest in peace.
You’ve certainly earned it.
♪
Narrator: That same day,
a video was streamed online
in which netero announced
his resignation as chairman
of the hunter association,
effective immediately,
and gave instructions
for choosing his successor.
It was drowned out by other news
from the government-run media.
Only a select few understood
that it was
his last will and testament.
Diego: Come. Raise a glass.
Let us drink
to this creature called man.
Good, evil, both are repeated
over and over
in an endless cycle,
the great spiral of time,
where a lifetime
is too long for peace,
yet too short for war.
That is why they yearn
and why they foster.
If they only knew
that all one needs in life
is the sun, the soil,
and of course poetry.
Palm: It’s over.
♪
( Komugi humming a tune )
Well, then it feels like you
and I haven’t played in forever.
Playing in real life’s
completely different
from playing in dreams.
- Meruem: True.
- Komugi: I could have sworn
I felt someone
kick me really hard
right in the stomach.
After that, there was this
strange person who kidnapped me.
And then you must have saved me,
dear leader, so thank you.
Meruem: It wasn’t me.
Thank my guards.
Komugi: Oh, no! I was wrong?
I’m sorry. I jumped
to the wrong conclusion.
Meruem: The fact is
they were too good for me.
Komugi: I’ll have to remember
to thank them when they stop by.
Meruem: I will relay
your gratitude.
I will see them soon.
( Komugi murmuring )
Meruem: Yes, I know.
Let’s begin.
Komugi: Okay!
Meruem: There was a time
you asked for my name.
Komugi: Uh, yes.
Meruem: Meruem.
My name is meruem.
Queen: Meruem.
It means the light
that illuminates all.
Komugi: Your name
is lord meruem?
( Gasps )
My name is komugi, lord meruem.
It’s such a great honor
to make your acquaintance.
Meruem: I know it is.
But, no...
( Thinking )
That’s a lie.
I knew nothing.
The truth of the matter is
I didn’t understand
what truly mattered.
Komugi: Um, lord meruem, i--
- meruem: Just meruem.
- Komugi: But--
meruem: Do not make me
repeat myself, komugi.
Komugi: I’m sorry,
but I could never do that.
I wouldn’t dare address you
so casually, dear leader!
Meruem: Silence.
If I beat you at gungi,
you will no longer use
the honorific.
( Komugi gasps )
I understand.
But if I address you without it,
is that when I die?
Meruem: Ah, that’s right.
There is no need
for you to die.
See, I am not the same
as I was before,
so you should be prepared
for innumerable losses.
Komugi: Right!
Meruem: What do you want
if you win?
You may choose your prize.
Komugi: I know.
I want another match.
Meruem: Foolish question.
Let us begin.
One-five-one, king.
Komugi: Nine-nine-one, king.
Meruem: Seven-nine-one, soldier.
Komugi: Two-three-one, soldier.
Meruem: Two-seven-two, Cannon.
Could it be?
Komugi: Seven-one-two, fort.
Meruem: This is kokoriko?
Komugi, are you mocking me?
Komugi: No.
Meruem:
Choose your words carefully.
I will not tolerate nonsense.
Komugi: No. It’s gungi.
I never joke when I play gungi.
Meruem: Very well.
You lose,
and I will take your life.
Komugi: Yes.
( Piece taps )
Meruem: Is she saying this will
not mean her certain death?
She had a number
of other options,
but all of them would only serve
to lengthen the game
without increasing her chances.
( Piece taps )
If she thinks
there’s an escape...
Nine-two-one, new Duke.
Now show me...
What lies beyond.
( Piece taps )
Komugi: Four-six-two, shinobi.
Meruem: Th-this is...
She found a way out.
Komugi: That night,
that’s when I came up with it.
Meruem: Silence.
I need some time to think.
♪
Here. It’s the only way.
She can’t checkmate this.
The more she tries,
the more the game
will turn in my favor.
But if she slows down
and allows me a turn to attack,
she won’t be able
to deflect the cavalry and Duke.
Two-six-one, cavalry.
A novelty buster. What now?
( Gasps )
What’s wrong? Why do you cry?
Komugi: Do i--
I mean, do I really
deserve to be so happy?
So many wonderful things
keep happening
to somebody like me.
Is that possible?
It doesn’t feel right
Meruem: I suppose
I must tell the truth.
You see, I have been poisoned,
and i’m dying.
Komugi: Please, no, lord meruem.
Meruem: I wanted to spend
my remaining moments...
Playing with you, komugi.
But this poison,
it’s contagious.
Stay by my side too long,
and you will also...
( Piece taps )
Wait. A novelty-buster buster?
Komugi: Lord meruem,
I want you to know
i’m so happy right now.
I may not be worthy,
but please let me go with you.
♪
Meruem: Yes, I see it now.
Komugi: I believe
that--that I was born
so I could be here today.
Meruem: This is why I was born,
for this moment.
♪
( Music playing only )
Meruem: Four-four-one, soldier.
Komugi: Six-five-one, cavalry.
Meruem: Two-seven-two,
new shinobi.
Komugi, are you there?
Komugi: Yes. I sure am.
I’m not going anywhere.
Four-five-one, Duke.
Meruem: That’s checkmate.
Komugi, are you there?
Komugi: Yes, yes, i’m here.
Let’s play another match.
The loser goes first.
Meruem: Komugi.
Komugi: Yes? What is it?
Meruem: It would appear
that I never defeated you,
not even once.
Komugi: What are you
talking about?
Come on.
We’re just getting started.
Meruem: Perhaps.
One-five-one, king.
Komugi: Nine-five-one, king.
Meruem: Komugi, are you there?
Komugi: Of course I am.
Go ahead.
It’s your turn, lord meruem.
Meruem: I feel rather...
Tired.
I shall sleep
just a short while.
But if I may make one request,
will you keep holding my hand?
Komugi?
Komugi, are you there?
Komugi: I can hear you.
All right. Like this?
Meruem: I shall wake up shortly.
Will you stay
by my side until then?
Komugi: I’ve never
left your side.
Don’t worry.
We’ll always be together.
Meruem: Komugi.
Komugi: Yes, yes? What is it?
Meruem: Thank you.
Komugi: You’re welcome.
Meruem: Will you...
Komugi: Yes?
Meruem: Will you say my name
one last time?
Komugi: Good night, meruem.
It’ll be all right.
I’ll be joining you soon.
♪