♪
Neferpitou: Sire.
( Singing in Japanese )
♪
Narrator:
Youpi’s attack succeeded
in splitting up
the extermination team.
( Limbs whipping )
He completely destroyed
the central staircase
and stood ready to engage
anyone who dared climb it.
Behind him were knuckle
and meleoron,
who had barely managed
to make it to the second floor.
And below...
The ones hit
at the closest range
by youpi’s attack were shoot...
Shoot: This is bad.
My leg is destroyed.
Morel: Shoot!
Narrator: ...And morel.
Morel: The rest is up to you.
Knuckle.
Narrator: He couldn’t
say knuckle’s name out loud.
Menthuthuyoupi: Huh?
♪
( Morel grunts )
Menthuthuyoupi: Huh?
( Grunts ) Stupid tricks!
Narrator: One attack by youpi
tore apart
the deep purple puppets,
but morel had
deliberately positioned them
with that exact possibility
in mind.
Menthuthuyoupi: Hmm?
They were just...
Decoys?!
This resistance...
That’s not smoke.
Huh?
Only the weapon
wasn’t made of smoke?
Get back here!
You fool!
Narrator: After using
his own weapon as a decoy,
morel was left with
no alternative but to run.
However...
♪
Knuckle knew exactly what to do
without being called.
Knuckle: Hakoware:
Bankruptcy chapter seven!
Damn. I’m giving it all i’ve got
to send him
flying over the horizon...
But he’s just at 590?
( Groans )
Ten seconds feels
like an eternity right now.
Narrator: Hakoware:
Bankruptcy chapter seven
accrues interest as time passes,
including any additional
damage received.
Menthuthuyoupi: Hmm?
I lost him.
Damn you!
Narrator: Youpi was enraged,
but was brought
back to his senses
when his extra eyes
glimpsed the hint of a shadow.
Shoot, his right leg crushed,
unconsciously used
his remaining leg
to stand on one
of his own fists.
Despite the fact
that he had never attempted
this technique before,
shoot realized that this
would be his signature move.
And although he had
no clear reason to do so,
he covered his right eye.
He simply enjoyed
how the feeling
of being cornered
filled him with a strength
that, up until now,
had eluded him.
( Menthuthuyoupi growls )
Narrator: Sustained
by adversity itself...
Menthuthuyoupi: Hmm?
Narrator: Shoot took flight.
His ferocious speed
and unparalleled drive
succeeded on forcing youpi
to focus on defense
for a fraction of a second...
All to help the others advance.
♪
Morel: Shoot, knuckle...
Once this is all over,
let’s drown ourselves
in really good liquor
and get wasted.
I wanna give you guys
a big hug,
and that’s the only way I can
think of to make you let me.
Narrator: The massive amount
of dust that was created helped
diffuse morel’s smoky aura
throughout the palace.
This allowed him
to monitor the situation
easily and discreetly.
Morel’s target
was in the throne room.
When youpi destroyed
the central stairway,
gon and killua
evaded the attack,
and without a single word
spoken between them,
they simultaneously
changed direction.
( Running footsteps )
Narrator: They planned to jump
directly from the second floor
of the right tower
to the third floor
of the central tower.
Upon hitting the ground,
they passed ikalgo
in the courtyard
as he headed for the elevator
to take him to the basement.
Ikalgo’s ability
lets him control corpses
like parts of his own body.
Forbidden games:
Living dead dolls
gave him the use
of flutter’s eyes,
which allowed him
to dodge dragon dive.
At that moment,
out of the corner of his eye...
Killua saw two soldier ants...
Headed in ikalgo’s direction.
It was then that killua
found himself running.
♪
Ikalgo: Huh?
Killua? Why’s he running
to the elevator?
Killua: What am I doing?
What’s wrong with me?
Narrator: Naturally,
he was rather perplexed
at his own actions.
He had always been
the one reminding others
of the importance
of staying on task.
Killua’s thought processes
ground to a halt.
Although his mind
was in a panic...
His body continued to act
in a rational manner,
extending only
the minimum of aura
that was absolutely necessary...
Combining speed
with the utmost accuracy.
He eliminated
the two soldier ants’s options,
as well as their
ability to fight.
♪
The only witnesses
were ikalgo and another ant.
Killua: Damn it.
What the hell?
What have I done?
( Gasps )
Ikalgo: Killua...
You owe me one.
Narrator: As he began
to return to his senses,
various emotions swirled
inside killua’s mind,
but ikalgo’s words were
just enough to dispel the chaos.
By the time the two ants
crashed to the ground,
killua was focused once again
and perfectly in control.
Welfin: Flutter?
Something’s wrong.
Narrator: The elevator
to the basement
was in a hallway
with rooms for servants
located at both ends.
Unfortunately
they were currently
occupied by soldier ants.
Ikalgo raced past the two ants
as quickly as possible,
and at the very moment that he
finally reached the elevator...
( Door opens )
( Ikalgo, flutter’s voice ) Hmm?
Narrator: Both doors suddenly
and simultaneously opened,
as if on cue,
and from the darkness,
two figures emerged.
♪
Ikalgo: Cheetu.
And bloster.
Narrator: Welfin saw flutter
and slipped out of sight,
because his instincts told him
that something was amiss.
Welfin: That was too fast.
The two soldier ants
saw an enemy,
sent out an alert,
and then died immediately.
The intruder who killed them
went back to where he came from.
The time between that and
flutter coming down the hall,
it was too short.
Ah, there’s only one explanation
I can think of.
Flutter and the intruder
must have passed each other.
But why would the intruder
have killed the peons,
but left flutter
alive and untouched?
Is flutter on the enemy’s side?
If so, he’s a traitor.
Is he acting on his own,
or was it under hagya--
I mean leol’s orders?
♪
Shaiapouf: How pathetic.
You weren’t by his side
when it mattered.
And you call yourself
a royal guard?
You don’t even know
where he is.
How do you qualify
as a royal guard?
No...
You fail as a royal guard.
It’s that simple.
Narrator:
Pouf’s unwavering devotion
was both his strength
and his weakness.
He had an absolute ideal
to live up to
with no room for amendment.
( Shaiapouf laughing )
Pouf, the former royal guard!
So, pouf, incompetent pouf,
you utter dimwit,
you fail as a royal guard!
Where will you go now?
You don’t know, do you?!
If the king isn’t
where you head to,
you will be less
than incompetent!
No, pouf, scum of the earth,
the truth is you just
don’t want to admit it.
You don’t want him
to be with that woman.
♪
Narrator: His emotions
were directed at the king,
as well as himself.
An absolute king feeling
concern for a lowly human,
lowering himself
to visiting the chambers
of human scum by choice!
It’s unforgiveable!
Still, that’s probably
where he is.
You knew that much
even before you got here.
You fail as a royal guard
not because you didn’t know
his whereabouts, far from it.
You fail, because you did know,
and, in spite of that,
you chose
not to rush to his aid.
You’re a traitor, pouf.
You’re lower than an insect.
You’re beneath trash,
and of course you mustn’t expect
anything from yourself now.
Therefore, you must
expect nothing from the king.
You must devote yourself
solely to the king.
For the king. For the king.
For the king!
For the king! For the king!
Narrator:
For a few brief seconds
after arriving
in the throne room,
a mad fanaticism
greatly hampered
pouf’s normal thought processes,
and he struggled
to compose himself.
Shaiapouf: I must go
to the king’s side.
Morel: Hey.
Ignoring me?
( Thuds )
Going straight
to the king’s side, huh?
( Aloud ) Too bad for you.
I’ve got you closed in.
Shaiapouf: Then I must ask,
would you please let me out?
Morel: No can do.
Real sorry about that.
Shaiapouf: I see.
( Morel growls )
( Bells tinkling )
Shaiapouf: Spiritual message.
♪
Gon: That’s morel’s smoky jail.
He said he’d use it
to keep pouf away from the king.
If it’s covering the entire
third floor of the tower,
then the king and pitou
aren’t there,
so where are they?
( Gon gasps )
( Gasps )
Netero: Hmm.
( Wind blowing )
♪
Narrator: Gon’s will to fight
had been set ablaze.
( Singing in Japanese )