[SARU] Lunar Edomae,
a talented young singer,
unexpectedly arrived at
Isono Eighth Junior High School,
sparking a fierce
rivalry with the
other popular
newcomer, Sun Seto.
Now the school has divided
itself into warring factions,
each supporting their
favorite of these two stars.
But who will win?
These moron boys have
gone completely crazy!
[NARRATOR]
Beneath the gently rolling
waves of the Seto Inland Sea.
Young Nagasumi's life is saved,
and forever changed.
But as with any debt,
this one too must be repaid.
So our story begins.
Please humor them with a smile,
for young love is never easy.
♪
[LUNAR DUDE B] There he is!
[LUNAR DUDE A]
Nagasumi Michishio!
[LUNAR DUDE B]
Don't let him get away!
[LUNAR DUDE A] Nagasumi!
[LUNAR DUDE B] Come back
here, you dirty little rat!
Why are you guys trying
to hunt me down, huh?
[LUNAR DUDE A] Because
Lunar likes you too much.
You're in the way!
[LUNAR DUDE B] We'll kill you,
and then we can have all
of precious Lunar's
love to ourselves!
[NAGASUMI] Let me go!
[LUNAR DUDE A]
Where did the rat go?
[LUNAR DUDE B] He won't escape!
[NAGASUMI THINKS] I can't
believe people really
get this hooked on pop stars.
[VOICES] You were, too.
[SUN DUDE A] There he is!
Nagasumi's over there.
What, now Sun's fans
are after me too?
[SUN DUDE A] Hey you, you'd
better stop right there, ya see.
[SUN DUDE B] Just who
do you think you are?
[SUN DUDE A] Ya see,
you're the one making it
hard for us all to
put the moves on Sun.
[SUN DUDE B]
So we gotta get you, ya see.
Leave me out of it! And what's
with the weird accents?
[MAWARI]
You there! Stop it!
[SUN DUDE A] It's the
disciplinary committee, ya see!
What exactly do you
idiots think you're doing?
Looks like you two are in
some serious need of discipline.
[SUN DUDE A]
You can stay out of this.
Don't you see Sun gives
us our reason for living?
[SUN DUDE B]
Even wilting flowers bloom
in the light of
the beautiful Sun.
[SUN DUDE A] She's our light!
Our light, don't ya see?
That, that's all nonsense!
No, ya see!This is true love!
You can make
your excuses later.
[NAGASUMI] I don't
understand what's
going on at this school.
[CLASS REP] N-Nagasumi
[NAGASUMI] Yes, Class Rep?
Nagasumi, you need
to come this way.
Um. What? Hey wait up,
I'm coming.
[NAGASUMI] Whew!
Hey thanks a lot for
saving my butt back there.
[MAWARI] Shut up!
[MAWARI] You can hang
onto your lousy thanks.
Who do you think is
responsible for this situation?
[NAGASUMI] What,
are you saying it's me?
I'm a member of the disciplinary
committee at this school.
This isn't discipline.
[NAGASUMI] I can
see your point there.
[MAWARI] According to my
reliable intelligence network,
this all started
because of a tug-of-war
between Lunar and Sun over you!
[GIRL A] Nagasumi
you're a total sleaze ball.
[GIRL B] You jerk!
[GIRL C] You womanizer!
[NAGASUMI] Gossip
sure spreads quickly.
[MAWARI] Excuse me?
No, what I
mean is your
intelligence network
is very impressive.
Nagasumi, you really
are hopeless, aren't you? Well.
[NAGASUMI] Huh?
Which'll it be?
[NAGASUMI] Which will what be?
I'm asking you
to tell me which one
of the girls you choose,
Sun or Lunar?
[NAGASUMI] Um?
What does this situation
have to do with you?
[MAWARI] This whole
thing is escalating because
you won't take
a stand, you idiot.
Crap. This isn't
going well at all.
Help me!
[CLASS REP] Mawari,
I think you should calm down.
[MAWARI] This is just one of
the reasons why all men suck!
[GIRL 1] Nagasumi, you're slime.
[GIRL 2] The scum of the earth.
[GIRL 3] The enemy
of all womankind.
Let's get him.
Why's this happening?
[SUN] Come on, Lunar.
We should stop this, okay?
But we can't. It's out
of our hands now.
Sun, I don't want
to see harm come to
my fans any more than you do.
But this battle can't possibly
end like this, you know.
Not until I have victory!
[LUNAR DUDES] Hail.
Lunar! Hail. Lunar! Hail!
I still don't understand
why we had to
start a fight like
this in the first place.
[Lunar laughs]
Because there's only
room for one heroine.
[SUN] Okay. Let's just
say you're it then.
[LUNAR] That pathetic,
laid-back attitude of yours
really pisses me off,
you know that?
Okay, Lunar.
[Nagasumi cries out]
They threw
me to the wolves!
[SUN DUDE A] It's Nagasumi!
[SUN DUDE B] Let's make
him a sacrifice for Sun!
[LUNAR DUDE A]
Don't let the rat escape!
[LUNAR DUDE B] Hunt
Nagasumi down and kill him!
[Teacher A laughs]
It's good to see how
energetic the kids are.
They've got a youthful
zeal to them these days.
You know, I haven't
seen Mr. Seto in a while.
Come to think of it,
I haven't seen him or his
family in some time.
Teachers get
such freedom here.
So considerate
of them, isn't it?
[Nagasumi out of breath]
I finally gave
them the slip.
That oughta teach
them to come after me.
[SARU] Nagasumi Michishio!
Aw come on just
leave me alone!
[NAGASUMI] Wait,
I recognize that voice.
[NAGASUMI] Chimp!
Wait, what are you doing
standing on a telephone pole?
Listen well
to me, Nagasumi.
Running away isn't going
to solve anything for you.
Nothing at all, do you hear me?
[NAGASUMI] What are you
talking about, monkey boy?
Running away's obviously
my only choice right now!
[SARU] Now is the
time to face yourself.
[NAGASUMI] Huh?
You have to
overcome this, boy.
If you can't then you
will have no future.
[NAGASUMI] Awakening!
Chimp. Instruct me.
Tell me what should I do now?
You must find the
path, Nagasumi.
Everyone is divided.
You are the only one
who can intercede
with both Lunar and Sun now.
This school's last
hope resides in you!
[NAGASUMI THINKS]
I understand now, Roshi.
I have to find some way
to make peace with them.
This fight is ridiculous.
It has to end.
Go to them, Nagasumi.
Fight your hardest, Nagasumi.
I can see it all clearly.
Fulfill your destiny,
and you will become a
great warrior who
will guide all your people.
[Nagasumi panting]
[NAGASUMI] Sun!
[medical machines beeping]
[NAGASUMI] Maki.
[MOM] Nagasumi?
[NAGASUMI] Sun,
what happened to her?
Maki was in a fight
with Lunar's bodyguards.
[REN] I'm sure she
fought well, but they
must have been too much for her.
[REN] Apparently she thought Sun
would be worried so she hid.
Sun just found her a while ago.
Oh Miss Sun. I'm
so sorry, so sorry.
Maki.
[REN] She's been talkin'
in her sleep for a while.
[GOZABURO] We just finished
treatin' her not long ago.
[GOZABURO] Those
wounds are serious.
[GOZABURO] Hey Maki.
Don't you think it's
about time we taught
those damn Edomae
a thing or two
about how we yakuza
settle our scores?
[GOZABURO]
We're hittin' the mattresses.
[NAGASUMI AND MOM]
You're kidding!
I won't forgive them if they
come crawling to beg for it.
Nothin' can stop me now!
Nagasumi, I must
ask you and your mother,
to stay away from this battle.
I do hope you understand.
[MASA] This isn't as simple as a
fight between Lunar and Maki.
A Seto member was taken down
by a member of
the Edomae family.
It's best settled between
just our two families.
Really Ren?
We'll do our
best to avoid
causin' ya any
trouble with this.
Please go about
your normal lives.
But we--
[SUN] Right now I'm gonna go
and take care of Lunar myself.
No, hold on Sun. We
don't need more violence!
I hate violence, too.
You know this isn't what
I wanted to happen.
But a good friend of
the family's been hurt,
and I'm not gonna
take that quietly, so--
[NAGASUMI] Aren't
I your husband, Sun?
Doesn't that make me a
part of the Seto gang too?
I can't just let
my entire family
be put in danger like this.
[GOZABURO] Did ya call
yerself her husband, maggot?
I know you're right
about this, Nagasumi.
But what now?
What else can I possibly
do to stop Lunar?
[rolling thunder in
the distance]
[NAGASUMI] This is
a message from Sun.
We'll fight this with songs.
Oh, what an amusing
plan Sun thought up.
Well all right then... of
course if we win the fight.
We trust you'll
agree to become our
manservant and leave
Sun once and for all.
And, and if you
lose, what then?
Oh come on.
As if we could possibly
lose to that silly girl.
[SARU] The big storm,
of angry, raging battle.
It comes.
The battle of the
great age of gods...
Begins now!
[LUNAR THINKS] A mermaid's voice
is her pride and her weapon.
Our singing is everything
to us. We can't lose.
Lunar it's packed!
The house is just packed!
[KAMATA] Really, I didn't know
what had gotten into you.
First you skip work for days.
And then you,
the darling celebrity
of the entire nation,
ask to do a surprise
concert in some little
junior high school?
As soon as I announced
it yesterday,
I was drowned in phone calls
from the talk shows
and the news.
[LUNAR] The stage is set.
We've waited so
long for this day.
And the wait has
been a painful one,
but it's here at last.
Here and now.
We'll finally take
Sun Seto down.
We've spent years
of mortification,
of humiliation, of deep shame.
Long, long years of
losing unfairly to that
talentless brat in
children's singing contests.
[KAMATA THINKS] I've never
seen Lunar so fired up before.
I think I owe this
Sun girl my thanks.
We'll pay her back
for all of those lost years.
We'll pay her back double.
After tonight, she won't
know what hit her.
[Lunar laughs insanely]
[LUNAR] All right, everyone...
This is how the contest
is going to work.
Sun and I will
take turns singing.
And once we're finished,
we'd like all of you to let us
know which one you liked best.
[LUNAR] The girl with
the most votes will win.
Ya rotten cheater!
Ya filled this place with
reporters who'll be on yer side!
Please Boss, you need
to cool it down man.
Yes, sir,
please calm down.
Sing like the angel
you are, Sun.
There's no way you can lose!
It's starting!
I'm going to sing
my song first, okay?
Go!
[LUNAR] One! Two!
One, two, three, go!
♪ People say
that I come from ♪
♪ the far end of
the universe ♪
♪ Because I'm so amazing I must
be some kind of super girl, ♪
♪ She's so incredible
she's Lunarian, ♪
♪ She is invincible
she's Lunarian ♪
♪ Well listen up 'cause ♪
♪ I've got somethin'
startlin' I'd like to reveal, ♪
♪ To all the people
in the solar system, ♪
♪ every rumor has been real ♪
♪ I am incredible,
I'm Lunarian ♪
♪ I am invincible,
♪ It's up to you if
you want to believe ♪
♪ Let your feelings
choose the final course ♪
♪ Don't, don't, give up
on your dreams ♪
♪ Let's make it exciting, ♪
♪ Fire up your engines, ♪
♪ Five, four, three,
two, one! ♪
♪ Take off! ♪
She's doin all right.
Pretty good, I guess?
[NAGASUMI THINKS]
Wow...
This is a lot different
than the tv taping.
She's performing on
a whole other level.
Does Lunar become
a better singer every day?
Who's side are you
on here, anyway,
you maggoty
piece of shit?
[NAGASUMI] I'm on
Sun's side, of course.
♪ Go, go to the moon
and then some ♪
♪ We can wish on every star,
just come with me ♪
[KAMATA THINKS] I've never
seen her like this before!
Lunar's staggering today.
She's such a pro,
it's unbelievable!
[LUNAR} ♪ Jump! Ooo jump! ♪
Hey, everyone, thank you!
Okay, now it's Sun's
turn to sing her song.
[LUNA FANS]
Encore! Encore! Encore!
Aw! In that case,
I'll sing one more song for you.
You let Sun sing!
It's her turn.
Can she do that?
You think Sun
can beat that song?
Course she can!
The Edomae girl's good.
She's honed her skills
a lot over the years.
She will be hard to defeat.
This is all yer fault
you damn maggot!
Now hurry up and do
something about it!
Oh, I think I can
see grandpa again.
[LUNAR THINKS]
We don't think we'll let you
have a turn to
sing tonight, Sun.
[LUNAR] After all,
since we announced
this to the media,
so many of our fans
flocked here that
they couldn't all fit inside.
If you can't see who'll win
the majority vote here,
you're a bigger idiot
than we thought.
And we don't believe
this is unfair at all.
[LUNAR] It's just
the way things are.
There will always be a
huge gap between someone
who's a national star like us,
and someone who's merely
a little school star like you.
[SUN] That's right.
Everything is fair in a fight.
[SUN] But I'll show
you that I can win
this without using
any dirty tricks,
and then you'll know
what Seto mermaids
are really made of, Lunar!
[LUNAR] Hah!
We're going to
finish this right now.
[LUNAR] What do
you think you're doing?
Stop copying us!
[SUN] I don't have
an album of popular
songs to choose
from like you do,
so I'll be takin' one of
yer songs instead.
Hope ya don't mind.
[LUNAR] You idiot!
Do you really think that a
copycat version will
beat the original?
[SUN] I told ya I was gonna
make this a fair fight.
We'll settle this
on even ground.
♪ The constellations confined
within my eyes start to dance ♪
♪ It feels like
stars could collide ♪
[LUNAR] That, that girl.
Her motions are
sloppy, but passionate.
On stage she almost
looks better than Lunar!
♪ ...and now I have
to believe in good luck! ♪
Get on camera two!
Follow that Sun girl!
[TV DUDE B] Right.
[GOZABURO] Sun!
[NAGASUMI] Sun, go!
Yeah, woo-hoo!
[LUNAR DUDE A] Hey!
Don't copy Lunar's song!
[LUNAR DUDE B]
You're playing dirty.
Get off the stage!
[LUNAR FANS] Boo!
♪ Feel the beating
of my heart ♪
♪ The rhythm of my melody ♪
♪ It's more than
just a song of love, ♪
♪ it's how you make me feel ♪
♪ Oh, you are so real to me ♪
Stay with me, man!
You'll die if you fall asleep!
♪ That's how I know it
will reach you one day ♪
♪ Past, present, future,
no matter where you turn to ♪
[LUNAR] She took our song!
How dare she!
Our songs. Our songs
are all that we have.
She took them!
She took them from us!
♪ No matter how far our hearts,
we'll never stay apart ♪
♪ Your love pulls
me close to you ♪
♪ It's your gravitation ♪
Why did Lunar have
to start singing too?
Sun had this locked up!
Miss Sun decided to show
her opponent some kindness.
Kinda naïve
of her, I guess?
You're wrong.
She made a promise.
[LUNAR] Think you're
doing us a favor?
[SUN] Nope, no favors.
To settle this once
and for all, ya see,
we both have ta sing
with all that we got.
[LUNAR] You're so naive.
[SUN] I'm just tryin' ta
end this fight peacefully.
Ya see. I made a
promise to Nagasumi.
Amazing, pushing each
other further and further.
This concert is truly--
[FANS]
What beautiful voices!
What the hell's going on?
Everyone's acting
really strangely.
The magic of mermaid
voices, I guess?
[NAGASUMI] Huh?
Aw man.
The mermaids'
singing voices directly
affect neuron reactions
in the brain and all.
The human mind is
too fragile to handle this.
Then what about me?
How am I okay?
Built up a
tolerance, I guess?
Oh, well that's great.
So I'm growing progressively
less human then, am I?
[NAGASUMI] Uh-oh!
The screen is full of people
doing stuff we can't show on tv!
[SHARK] So this is what happens
when a human's brain breaks?
[GOZABURO]
Yeah, it looks like it.
[MASA] It would seem the
hormones are certainly flowing.
[MAWARI] We've found
the root of this evil.
Right!
It's time to finish this.
I'm going to teach these guys
a lesson about discipline!
[GIRLS] Yeah!
Discipline and the
rules of this society.
[MAWARI] Now charge, girls!
[MAWARI] We arrived too late.
[CLASS REP] Um,
I don't think our
speed was the issue here.
[MAWARI] Let's just
burn the place down.
[CLASS REP] No.
Our, our fans!
What's happening to them?
[SUN] Oh dear.
[LUNAR] They've become
unbroadcastable.
[BOY B] Sing another
song, Lunar!
[BOY C] Please,
please we'll do anything!
Sun! You've ruined
our big concert.
How dare you!
What? So does
that mean I won, Lunar?
No way! We can't
believe you worthless
humans were totally taken
in by Sun's pathetic singing.
If she can turn you into a
pitiful mess like this,
you should see what we can do.
We'll show you the true
terror of mermaid singing!
No, Lunar! You can't
lose your temper!
All right everyone.
Next up, we have
the song of war.
Ha!
[LUNAR]
♪ Come and stand with me ♪
♪ Waken from
your sleep, rise up ♪
♪ Let you rage reign free ♪
♪ Let your hatred
be your guide now ♪
That damn girl! How could
she do something like this?
[SHARK] She should
have just done
that from the
beginning, I guess?
[NAGASUMI] She shouldn't've.
[SUN] Nagasumi!
Tell me this song isn't
a weapon of some kind!
It's a powerful
mermaid weapon
used to control
people's minds!
[KAMATA] At this rate,
it'll become a blood bath!
[NAGASUMI] Hey Sun,
can't you counter this
with a song that will
calm everybody down?
Like a "song of peace"
or something, maybe?
We need to make Lunar stop!
Impossible!
No one can stop Lunar
once she's gotten like this!
Besides, the song of war that
she's singing is
incredibly powerful.
No simple song is going
to work against it now.
Nagasumi, you
have to stop the fighting!
But, I'm not the
man for the job.
A simple song's not
gonna cut it, but, maybe.
What, did you think
of one that will work?
Ya see, if ya help me,
I think we might be
able to do somethin'
If we work
together, Nagasumi,
we should be able to stop this.
[NAGASUMI] As long
as we're together,
Sun, I know we can do anything.
[SUN] All right then.
Here goes nothin'.
[SUN] Ancient mermaid lyrics!
Song of the Hero!
Go!
You're still daring
to interfere with us, Sun?
[SUN] You're the only
one who can help them.
Just you, Nagasumi.
[SUN] You're the only one who
can make them understand.
It's up to you now.
[LUNA FAN] Annihilate them!
[SUN FAN] You're gonna die now!
[SUN] Hearts
transform into bonds
[SUN DUDE A]
What's with this guy?
[LUNAR DUDE A] Who
cares? Let's just get him!
Crush them all!
[NAGASUMI] I'm a dragon.
Back off, all of you!
Unless you think you can
stand up to the
full power of my fist.
[SARU] The storm has come. Now!
[SUN DUDE B] What, did
you come out of a manga?
[LUNAR DUDE B]
Don't try to mess with us!
[STUDENT A] Whoa!
He's fighting off three
people with one hand?
Wow. When did Nagasumi
become so incredibly strong?
[STICK FIGURE A]
Attack all at once!
[STICK FIGURE B] We'll
come at him from all sides.
[STICK FIGURES] He got us!
[NAGASUMI] I thought
I told you to back off.
[FANS] We're sorry!
And we've decided we
can't win this anymore.
We'll give up now.
A great warrior.
[LUNAR] What the hell is this?
It's love.
Kamata! Our special
performance.
It was completely ruined.
There, there, my dear.
[SUN] Lunar.
[LUNAR] Why are you
glaring at me like that?
You look so mean!
You don't, you don't
hate me now do you?
Our battle is over.
Now, you come over
and apologize to Maki,
and then we can put
all of this behind us.
[LUNAR] Maki?
Do you mean the little conch?
[SUN] Yes, her!
And what justification did
you have to hurt her so badly?
But I didn't.
I didn't do anything to her!
--Huh?
--So who then?
Ya actually have the nerve
to deny it, ya brat?
[MAKI] Please, boss, hold on.
[ALL] Maki?
Jeez, what happened here?
You guys sure did
a number on this place.
Miss Sun.
The truth is,
the day that Lunar first
showed up at the
Michishio residence.
[MAKI] Well if
it isn't Miss Lunar.
It's been a long time.
What brings you
here all of a sudden?
Oh shut it, Maki.
We're here because
we're graciously deigning
to pay a little visit to
Sun Seto, that's all.
Now move over.
We're coming through.
No one gets through unless
Maki the Conch allows them to!
Take my Jet Ram Attack!
[BOB] Kamikaze!
[MICHAEL] That'll leave a mark.
[LUNAR] Yeah.
We'll do you a favor
and pretend we
didn't see that.
It has to be embarrassing.
[MAKI] Thank you.
It was embarrassing.
I didn't know how to tell you.
Ugh...
what did you do?
You mean she
did it to herself?
You made a hell
of a mess girl.
[SHARK] You call
yourself an assassin?
[SUN] Oh well,
it was a good fight!
Yeah, a real good fight!
[LUNAR] What's going on?
Did we do all that for nothing?
[SUN] Never mind!
Let's just forget it.
[NAGASUMI THINKS] So Lunar isn't
a horrible person after all.
[KAMATA] Lunar!
Aren't you ready yet?
[LUNAR] We overslept.
Lunar, chew slower.
You're going to choke yourself.
But I'm not used
to eating this early.
I don't usually
eat any breakfast.
We eat breakfast
in this house.
Can't I just take a
vitamin or something?
As long as you
live under my roof,
you're going to eat
a proper breakfast.
Aw!
[NAGASUMI] I can't believe it.
My mom's done the impossible.
She can actually control Lunar.
Lunar, does this
mean that you're
really going to live
here with all of us?
We've simply decided
that perhaps
it would be interesting
to try living the
commoner's life for a
little while, that's all.
You realized you were
going to miss us, huh?
No. Our manservant
isn't broken in yet.
We can't leave.
You should be grateful.
Why are you laughing
at us? Idiots!
♪
[NAGASUMI] Now Lunar's
crashing at our house too.
Two new girls in the house!
Boy am I lucky!
I'll take my responsibility
seriously and protect them!
Of course no
sooner do I say that
than a new enemy shows up.
A third mermaid?
Wait, it's a guy?
And he's taking Sun?
Now hold on just a second!