[LUNAR] ♪ My heart
beats a symphony, ♪
♪ Your love inspires me, ♪
♪ That's how I know
I'll be with you one day ♪
♪ No matter how far our hearts
will never stay apart, ♪
♪ Your love pulls
me close to you ♪
♪ It's your gravitation! ♪
[ANNOUNCER]
That was Lunar with her
heart stopping single
"Gravitation."
Thank you, everybody!
[Lunar laughs]
[LUNAR THINKS] Everyone
adores our songs.
What a wonderful feeling!
[CROWD] Lunar!
I love you, Lunar!
[LUNAR THINKS]
That's right, humans.
Bow down before
the power of our songs.
[NARRATOR]
Beneath the gently rolling
waves of the Seto Inland Sea.
Young Nagasumi's life is saved,
and forever changed.
But as with any debt,
this one too must be repaid.
So our story begins.
Please humor them with a smile,
for young love is never easy.
♪
[Lunar laughs insanely]
[LUNAR] They were hypnotized
by our songs yet again.
Yes, pathetic humans,
that's right, worship us.
Bow down.
[KAMATA] Very good
work today, Lunar!
Yes? Oh, well thank
you very much!
[LUNAR] Oh.
It's just my manager,
and not an adoring fan.
At least knock next
time, would ya?
Lunar, you have
a full schedule
of commercials and
recording tomorrow,
so try to get to
bed early tonight.
You do need your sleep.
Yeah.
And, honey, one
other thing as well.
It's just something
that the don, uh,
something that the
company president told me.
[LUNAR] Papa, huh?
[KAMATA] That friend
of yours from childhood.
What was her name again?
Oh, yes, Sun from the Seto gang.
Well, it seems she's
moved to Saitama.
Maybe it would
be good for you
to pay her a visit
sometime soon.
Wouldn't you like to say 'hi'
to your old friend, Lunar?
[ LUNA] Kamata,
I need you to cancel
all of my appointments
for tomorrow.
Yes, of course.
[KAMATA] Wait, Lunar,
what's gotten into you?
Sun Seto.
[LUNA (YOUNG)]
♪ This is not the way ♪
♪ romance is
supposed to be. ♪
♪ Love is worth the risk 'cause
we have nothing left to lose. ♪
♪ Think of everything
love gives us in return! ♪
[LUNAR (YOUNG)]
Thank you!
Bye now!
[Lunar laughs]
[LUNAR (YOUNG)] A mermaid's
true weapon is her voice.
Her sweet song.
A good voice is the
greatest badge of pride,
and there is no mermaid
anywhere out there
who can sing better
than Lunar Edomae!
[WAITRESS]
Don't know what it is,
but that kid's got
one creepy laugh.
[MOBSTER A]
There's another girl singing.
Listen to her.
[SUN (YOUNG)]
♪ Momotaro-san, Momotaro-san ♪
♪ Can you share
your dumplings? ♪
♪ Will you share
them with me? ♪
[MOBSTER B]
I don't understand what
this girl is doing to me.
I can't stop crying.
Yeah, it's tearin' at some
wound deep inside'a me.
Her voice is so sweet
and innocent I can't take it.
I'll share them
with you dear little Sun.
Maybe we should
all try to be more
like that and
share our dumplings.
[MOBSTER A] I've
never heard another
child sing as well
as Lunar before.
[MOBSTER B] And the winner
of tonight's singing contest is,
Sun from the Seto gang!
Someone who
thinks they can
sing better than us
cannot be tolerated.
We'll teach you, Sun Seto.
[SARU] I can't believe Sun made
us go home without her.
This sucks.
She said that
she was going to
be helping out the class rep,
so we just have to accept it.
And you didn't volunteer
to help them out?
Nah, they said they were setting
up for tomorrow's health class.
Now that I wouldn't
mind helping with.
Think of all
the cool secrets you
could learn about
girls' bodies there.
Oh, I almost forgot.
[SARU] Holy freaking
crap on a stick!
This is a Lunar souvenir that
you can only get at concerts!
[SARU] B-But how
did you get this? How?
[NAGASUMI] Oh,
I got it yesterday when I
went to watch her
tape a concert for tv.
You mean you
won a ticket?
No one gets those!
Do you know how lucky you are?
You have been truly blessed.
Are you a unicorn?
You can keep
that little token,
you poor schmuck who didn't
get to see Lunar
performing live.
You think maybe
you're letting
this go to your head, huh, kid?
She sings so well, but she's
got such an amazing
personality, too.
I know! She's so
sweet and humble
in the face of
her great success.
I'm going to her
next concert, also.
And I'll have a
good seat this time!
Now, you hold
on a second there.
Should you be
saying that...?
After all, what would
Sun think about it, huh?
[SARU] You're living
with a girl that cute,
and your eye's still roaming?
Is she not enough for you?
It has nothing to
do with Sun.
No? I beg to differ.
Sun is a real girl, and Lunar
is a famous pop star.
You can't possibly
equate the two.
Oh, I see how it is,
so you've rationalized
your betrayal.
What a thoughtful guy
you are, Nagasumi.
Where did all this
rain come from?
[SARU] See ya.
I'm gonna go home now.
Yeah, okay.
I'll see you later.
[NAGASUMI] What's that?
[NAGASUMI] Hey!
Are you all right, miss?
Can I help?
What happened to you--
That's not a fish!
It's a mermaid collapsed in the
street who I don't even know!
[LUNAR] Stupid rain storm
came out of nowhere!
Oh good, so she's alive.
L-l-l-l-lu!
You saw me!
The random mermaid
is really Lunar!
[LUNAR] No!
[NAGASUMI THINKS]
This is insane!
What is Lunar
doing here?
Okay, better question,
Lunar's a mermaid?
[NAGASUMI] That was a
mermaid ultrasonic wave attack.
We're impressed you
know something like that.
What's going on?
You okay? The rain
came so sudden.
What you say Miss Lunar.
Did this human see something?
[LUNAR] He saw our true form.
Bob, Michael, we'll need to
take the human back with us.
Yes, Miss Lunar.
Not good.
I remember being
kidnapped like this before.
Um, uh.
What is it?
Should I assume
that I'm going
to be killed now that I've
seen your mermaid form?
My you do
catch on quickly.
[NAGASUMI THINKS] Why does
this keep happening to me?
[SUN] Stop it now.
[SUN] Yer talkin'
about horrible stuff
like killin' right in front
of my own house?
So now what's
all the fuss about?
My, the rain stopped
as suddenly as it started.
Long time no see.
Sun Seto.
I recognize you.
You're Lunar Edomae!
[LUNAR] That's right.
Your fearsome rival,
your arch nemesis,
the famous singer Lunar Edomea
has come to pay
you a visit, Sun.
[SUN] Wow, it's been
so long, Lunar!
Don't hug
us so familiarly!
So, when the hell
did you arrive here?
A respectful mermaid would've
come to see us long before now!
[SUN] Oh... sorry.
Lots of stuff happened,
and I kinda forgot about ya.
Ooh look! It's the
pretty little singer
from the yakuza
singing contests.
[SUN] Give back
Nagasumi now, please.
Oh yes,
of course, here.
I'll have you
know that we
never once forgot
about you, Sun!
We remember what you did to us!
[NAGASUMI THINKS]
This girl's a bit different
from the Lunar that I've seen.
You certainly seem used
to drying off tails, human.
[NAGASUMI]
You have no idea.
[Sun groans]
[LUNAR] Now there's something
I'd like to know about.
What sort of
relationship do
you have with this human?
[LUNAR] He saw your fins
so you agreed to marry him?
Impossible!
How could a noble
mermaid agree to
marry a lowly human?
[SUN] But there's
a really good story
about a mermaid
marryin' a human.
That story is fiction,
and it doesn't end well.
Why can't we get it over
with and kill him already?
Ya know, Lunar,
yer kinda mean.
That's exactly why Sun
took me into her family.
To avoid either
of us being killed.
Uh huh,
and your point is?
[NAGASUMI] So I won't
let you kill me, Lunar.
I'll do whatever I can
to stop you and I won't
go down without a fight.
I owe her that much.
My life belongs
completely to Sun now.
Thank ya, Nagasumi.
[SUN] What is it?
[LUNAR THINKS] We lost to
Sun in the singing contests.
Every single time.
[LUNAR] To us,
singing was everything.
To her, singing was nothing
but silly nursery rhymes.
To prove that we
were better than Sun,
we dedicated our
lives to singing.
We even entered the
entertainment industry
and struggled long and hard,
clawing our way to the top.
And when we came to her
to flaunt our musical success.
That girl.
She turns around and flaunts
this human boy in our face!
Why Sun? Why do
you always make us feel
bad about what
we don't have, huh?
What do you mean,
what you don't have?
In that case, Sun.
We'll take him.
We'll take that
husband of yours.
He saw us in our true
mermaid form, after all.
His puny life is
our rightful property.
Uh-oh. I don't
like this at all. Not good.
[LUNAR THINKS] That's right.
We'll steal Sun's happiness.
You're ours, human!
Just imagine for
the rest of your life,
you'll be our personal
manservant, my darling boy.
Uh-oh... I don't think I like
the sound of that much, either.
[SUN] I'll teach ya to try
and take what's mine!
I met Nagasumi a long
time before you did, Lunar.
You better back off right now!
Now, now it isn't a question
of chronology is it?
It doesn't matter
who caught him first.
We're just offering to help out.
We can protect him.
I refuse your offer.
I'm gonna be the one
to protect him. Ya see.
Let's go, manservant.
[SUN] Fat chance of that!
Nagasumi lives with me!
[NAGASUMI THINKS]
No way! It can't be true.
This girl isn't Lunar!
My Lunar is sweet
and modest and kind!
A servant's got
no home of his own!
He's not a servant!
Well, then I guess
he'll have to die!
Lunar you're taking this
rivalry thing too far!
Sun, you brat!
I see you're just as aggressive
and obstinate as ever, huh?
You're one to talk, Lunar!
I guess a girl
who comes all
the way to Saitama get married
has some fight in her yet.
Well, okay!
We'll show you
we can fight too!
Starting today,
we'll live in this house,
and we'll be in charge!
Then you'll realize we're
the master of all we see!
Just try 'n stop us.
Bring it on then you, cow!
No, there's no way. Lunar's
nothing like this girl.
That would just be silly.
[NAGASUMI] Oh, Lunar.
[alarm bell rings]
Aw man too bad.
Just a dream.
None of it was real.
For a second I was hoping that
Lunar really had come here.
Oh good morning
manservant.
[NAGASUMI THINKS]
But how could this happen?
This is like those stories
you hear about people
getting all drunk and
then waking up the
next day beside
some strange woman!
Okay, maybe that's
not the best analogy.
[NAGASUMI THINKS]
I'm so close to Lunar we're
actually breathing
on each other!
[SUN] Hey!
[NAGASUMI] Sun!
Lunar, I was wonderin'
where ya'd gotten off to!
[LUNAR] Damn.
Ya were supposed ta
be sleeping in my room!
What do 'ya think you're
doing in here with him?
[Lunar chuckles]
Tell me something, Sun.
Have you ever
slept with Nagasumi?
[NAGASUMI] Huh?
[SUN] I haven't.
[Lunar laughs]
[LUNAR] Well, then I
suppose we beat you to it!
We slept with your
husband before you!
[SUN] Slept with him?
She slept with him?
[SUN] Even though
I'm Nagasumi's bride,
I didn't get to
be his first kiss.
That kiss was stolen from
him this summer by Masa!
[NAGASUMI] Masa!
[SUN] And then my childhood
friend had an affair with him.
No one's leaving anything
for his promised bride!
[NAGASUMI] I think
'sleeping in the same bed'
is different from
'sleeping with.' Come home!
How lucky you
are to sleep with
your master on
the very first night.
Right manservant?
I'll admit that it
was a little exciting.
[Lunar laughs]
[LUNAR] You hear that?
[LUNAR] My manservant was
excited to sleep with me!
Nagasumi, I'm your bride!
What am I supposed
to do about this?
I don't think
there's anything
you can do about it, Sun.
Nothing Nagasumi?
Are you sure
there isn't anything?
[NAGASUMI THINKS] Whoa!
Sun's holding my
hands so tightly in hers.
I wonder what she
wants to do for me?
[LUNAR] You think you can
touch a mermaid's hands?
Behave yourself!
[LUNAR] Listen up.
You shouldn't have
survived the night.
By rights we should have
had you killed yesterday.
[LUNAR] But we have
mercifully decided to
allow you to live
as our manservant.
[NAGASUMI THINKS]
Somehow the situation
keeps getting worse and worse.
[LUNAR]
The Michishio family will
remain our servants for life.
You got that, you filthy human?
It's lively up there, huh?
Honey can you pass
the soy sauce?
[BOB] Yeah.
Oh, thank you.
[BOB] Soy sauce.
[DAD] Uh, what?
[BOB] Oh yes! Oh yeah!
Nice.
Nice singing.
It must be difficult to be
one of Lunar's bodyguards.
If you haven't eaten yet,
perhaps you'd
consider dining with us.
It'd be an honor to have you.
[MOM] Welcome to our happy home.
Yes, so happy.
[STUDENT 1] Hey!
Isn't that Lunar, the pop star?
[STUDENT 2] What's a celebrity
like her doing at our school?
[STUDENT 3]
Nagasumi's involved again.
What's with him?
[GOZABURO] I don't feel
good. Too bad I have class.
And now I'll
introduce a new
student who'll be joining us.
[NAGASUMI THINKS] I can't
believe Lunar got all the
transfer paperwork
done in one day.
The entertainment business
can sure pull strings.
Time to introduce
yourself,
only daughter of the
Edomae gang's boss.
So our homeroom
teacher is none
other than the boss of the
Seto gang and Sun's father.
It's nice to
meet all of you!
My name is Lunar Edomae.
I've transferred here
to this school for
various reasons that
really aren't important.
It's a pleasure to be here!
[GOZABURO] What the hell?
What's gotten into
all of the little brats?
Mister Seto,
are you saying
you don't know who Lunar is?
What? Of course
I know who she is.
She's the Edomae gang boss'--
What he means is that
we used to be neighbors.
Isn't that true, Mister Seto?
Uh, yeah, right.
What do you say, Sun?
Yeah, Lunar and I
were childhood friends.
Wow!
Sun, you're so cool!
Huh?
Why do you say that?
'Cause, you're childhood
friends with a celebrity!
I hope that we're
all going to be friends.
[room erupts in cheers]
[NAGASUMI THINKS]
Listening to Lunar today,
she seems really
sweet and cute again.
Yeah... What I saw earlier
must have been
some sort of hallucination.
[SARU] Nagasumi!
[NAGASUMI] Can I help you Chimp?
Only yesterday
you were talking about
how big a fan
you were of her,
and then today she just
miraculously appears
at our school?
What, did you stumble
across some sort of
magic lamp or maybe you gathered
the seven Dragonballs
or somethin'?
Try not to freak out when
I tell you, but, well, see...
I kinda became Lunar's
manservant somehow.
[SARU] Huh?
[NAGASUMI] I'm sure that you
understand my meaning, Chimp.
So that's how
this happened then?
You somehow went
from being her devoted,
screaming fan to being
her kinky love slave?
[SARU] Seriously?
[NAGASUMI] So, as of yesterday,
Lunar is living at my house.
A love nest!
Your house is now a
love nest, Nagasumi!
Wait, what the hell?
Where's the camera?
I know it's here somewhere!
It's okay, Chimp.
I don't understand
my meaning either.
Give me a break!
If being a slave meant
you got to live with a
celebrity 100 percent
of the world
would do it without a doubt!
And for now you're keeping
them both all to yourself?
[NAGASUMI] No, at least,
that isn't my intention.
Listen carefully
to what I'm about
to tell ya, kid, because
maybe your pathetic
pea-sized brain just
hasn't noticed this yet.
[SARU] Sun's got long, shiny
hair and beautiful eyes.
She's kind of spacey,
but let's face it,
men are attracted to that,
so she's become very popular.
Right now Sun's
shot to the top of the
chart as our school's
number one star.
Are you with
me here so far, kid?
Wha--.
Sun's a star here?
[SARU] And you live with her.
That's enough to
make any man jealous,
but it keeps getting worse
for us normal guys.
[SARU] Lunar's a star not
just here, but nationwide!
She's impish and
sexy and, above all,
blessed with an amazing voice.
Her albums consistently
top the charts.
She's the most popular
pop star out there!
[SARU] And now you're telling me
that you get to
live with her too?
[NAGASUMI]
No, you don't get it...
She forced her
way into my house!
[SARU] That just makes
me more jealous!
[SARU] Is all this world
offers to be yours alone?
And is the torrent of ardent
pathos yours alone as well?
[CLASS REP] Chimp,
could you get down?
We're in homeroom right now.
Your vocabulary really
expands when you
get excited
about something.
Looks like you
got all famous while
I wasn't paying
attention, Lunar.
My, you flatter us.
That wasn't
a compliment.
[GOZABURO] Now go
take the desk next to Sun.
Looks like we're gonna
be neighbors again, Lunar.
Yeah, it looks like it,
and we're honored to
be sitting next to you.
You've always
sorta followed me
around nippin' at my heels,
but ya do seem
more intense this time.
[LUNAR] Of course we're intense!
We've suffered humiliation
at your hands for too long!
We're getting sick of it.
[SUN] Really?
But when we appeared
on the music scene,
the entire country
acknowledged our greatness!
They loved me
from the first note I sang!
[LUNAR] Basically...
The judging at the
Children's Singing contest
was clearly screwed up.
It must've been rigged.
[LUNAR] Just you wait.
We'll show you how inferior
you are to us now, Sun.
[SUN THINKS] First the
thing with Nagasumi. Now this.
She really has lost
it this time, hasn't she?
[school bell chimes]
[LUNAR] Oh, this is terrible!
I just transferred,
so I have no text books.
What should I do?
Hey, if ya need
to ya can go
ahead and look on with me--
[BOYS] Please use mine!
Oh, thank you.
[LUNAR THINKS]
How do you like that, Sun?
That's how much people love us!
Oh no, what should I do?
I left my notebook back at home.
You're hopeless, Sun.
Here, use my--
[BOY A] Here, I have
some paper you can use.
[BOY B] No, here,
take my notebook.
[SARU] Just take my book bag!
Why does everyone
love her so much?
She's not even a star!
I had no idea Sun
was so popular.
How could I not notice that?
Ya get it now, Nagasumi?
[NAGASUMI] Chimp.
Now you're beginning to
see how it actually is.
There are plenty
of guys in this school
who care about
her more than you do.
[SARU] That's right, Nagasumi!
Never forget that love is war!
[NAGASUMI] Please
teach me Chimp Roshi!
[SARU] Huh?
It looks like a storm is
beginning to brew
in the distance.
Uh, you there, Sun Seto,
why don't you try solving it.
Yes sir.
[SUN] Um, uh.
[BOY A] Hang in there Sun!
[BOY B] You can do it.
You're a smart girl!
[BOY C] Sun!
I know Miss Sun
is popular,
but this much enthusiasm
is ridiculous.
[MASA] Okay, Lunar Edomae.
You try the next problem.
[Lunar fake weeps]
Hm?
What's wrong?
I'm sorry, Mister Masa.
I don't know it!
Come on now!
This is a pretty easy problem
to solve, you know.
[BOY A] How could say that
to a brand new student?
[BOY B] Yeah, poor Lunar!
[BOY C] That's mean,
giving her such a hard problem!
[BOY D] Apologize
to Lunar, you scumbag!
Hey now!
You don't have to be
so hard on Mister Masa!
[LUNAR] As if that problem
was actually difficult for us!
[CLASS REP] Stop shouting.
If you boys could
just calm down a little.
[MAWARI] Boys,
if you don't shut up soon,
you're all going to be
rounded up and arrested!
--[LUNA FACTION] Lunar! Lunar!
--[SUN FACTION] Sun! Sun!
[NAGASUMI] Uh oh...
What's going on with everyone?
[NAGASUMI] The class
has split into people
rooting for Lunar and
people rooting for Sun.
[MASA] Hey, these kids
are just ordinary humans.
What have you done
to get them like this?
Don't you think you're taking
your mischief a bit too far?
[LUNAR] Now, now,
we haven't done
anything to the children.
The boys are getting
excited all on their own.
What's a girl to do?
[Lunar laughs]
[LUNA FACTION] Lunar!
[SUN FACTION] Sun!
Has this been bottled
up inside everybody all along?
[SARU] Young Nagasumi,
you still don't understand.
[NAGASUMI] Chimp Roshi!
Lunar's transfer to
this school activated
the fans she's had
here the whole time.
[SARU] That triggered
the sentiments festering
inside Sun's own
fan base to leave
dormancy and
rise to the surface.
These two surges
have had the effect
of polarizing the class,
and the two groups
are now going to collide.
[NAGASUMI] What?
[BOY A] Are the two of you
siding with Lunar or Sun?
[SARU] This violent
maelstrom will
spread ever wider
as time passes.
Now that the great
tide of conflict
has begun, no one can stop it.
Isono Eighth Junior High School
will inevitably be rent in two.
[SARU] A new era
has begun now, Nagasumi!
What the hell
is going on here?
And what about
our classes?
[CLASS REP]
Boys are so volatile.
Are all you boys morons?
Stop now! Come on!
[Maki groans]
[MAKI] I'm coming, Miss Sun.
Maki's here. I'll help you.
Damn you Lunar!
[Lunar laughs wickedly]
[LUNAR] Yes, everything
is going according to plan.
[LUNAR]
Sun Seto, before long,
no one's going
to love you anymore.
♪
[NAGASUMI]
The plot is thickening!
Our school is
in serious danger of
being ripped apart
by senseless violence!
Warring factions
have taken over.
This is bad!
What should I do?
Lunar, why can't you go
back to being the sweet,
modest, talented girl you were?
Oh, that was never really you?
Damn celebrities.