[distant voices]
[music playing in the distance]
[NAGASUMI] Somebody!
[NAGASUMI]
Help me!
Somebody!
[NAGASUMI] Oh, god,
I'm gonna drown!
[NAGASUMI] I can't hold
my breath any longer!
Dammit!
I'm drowning!
Somebody help me please.
[angelic voices]
[NAGASUMI] A mermaid?
[NARRATOR] Beneath
the gently rolling
waves of the Seto Inland Sea.
Young Nagasumi's life is
saved, and forever changed.
But as with any debt,
this one too must be repaid.
So our story begins.
Please humor them with a smile,
for young love is never easy.
♪
[NAGASUMI] Hey,
dad, are we there yet?
You don't have
to actually answer that.
I just wanted you to
know how bored I am.
What's wrong with you?
You're too young to be bored.
Can't you even
sit still for ten minutes?
Well, I guess I take
after my parents.
Just try to relax.
We should be there
any minute now.
[NAGASUMI THINKS]
Summer vacation and here I am,
Nagasumi Michishio,
stuck visiting my grandmother.
Well, at least she lives
by the Seto Inland Sea.
[NAGASUMI]
Whoa, what?
You're kidding me, there's
only one bus every hour?
You surprised, city boy?
Well, it's really
not very convenient.
And they don't even run
the bus during the evening!
And that's just the way
we like it around here!
But I guess a city
boy from Saitama
wouldn't understand our
easygoing lifestyle.
Are you gonna call
me 'city boy' the whole trip?
Ignore him. He's just
a little excited to be back.
[NAGASUMI] Hey, Dad...?
Weren't we driving right
next to the sea a minute ago?
[DAD] Yep. It's just
beyond the trees there.
Seto is nothing but
mountains and water.
Not much in between.
The road's kind of narrow.
It looks like
we're gonna fall off.
I guess it has been
a while since your last visit.
You were only about
four or five years old.
[NAGASUMI] Yeah. I don't
remember much about it.
[ding]
Grandma,
was that right?
[GRANDMOTHER] You betcha!
That made your grandpa happy.
[NAGASUMI]
Oh... cool.
[GRANDMOTHER] I'm so
sorry ya had to make
dinner after
comin' all this way.
What kind of hostess makes
her guests do the cookin'?
Oh don't worry
about it, mother.
It's my pleasure. I only
wish that we could make
it out here to visit
you more often.
Yeah, my job's pretty
stringent with my time off.
[GRANDMOTHER]
Well you don't have ta' bring
yer stinkin' husband with you.
You and Nagasumi can come
on out any time ya want.
Jeez, mom... it's sure
good to see you too.
[MOM] Well,
Nagasumi's in school.
Today's actually the
first day of his vacation.
I know, I know.
Can we just forget about
school while we're here?
Thanks to his grades,
he spent the
last month in summer school.
You're lucky we decided to
wait and not leave without you.
Well thanks,
I love you too.
[MOM] He's not the
world's greatest student.
[grandmother laughs]
[GRANDMOTHER] That's nothin'.
I hardly doubt ya could be
any more lousy
of a student than yer
father was and yet here
he is, still alive and kickin'.
Stop picking on me.
[GRANDMOTHER]
And he managed to wind up
with the best wife in the world.
Thanks!
[GRANDMOTHER] And he's
got a cute little son.
Can't ask for more than that!
Hey, do you hear that?
You're cute and little.
And you're big and ugly.
[GRANDMOTHER] I'm sorry if my
son turned out to be a letdown.
I hope ya won't
hold it against me.
It's okay.
I'm sorry your grandson's
so disappointing.
[NAGASUMI AND DAD]
Ow! Come on!
[TV CHICK] And now
for the local weather.
It looks as though we're
going to have clear skies and
warm temperatures in the
Shikaku area tomorrow...
[DAD] Hey Nagasumi!
Clear skies tomorrow!
Perfect for swimming!
[NAGASUMI] You gonna
sleep in your bathing suit?
I can't believe how
hyperactive you've
been acting dad.
[DAD] Well, you're
not hyper enough!
Why don't you act like a kid?
Summer vacation will
be over before you know it!
You should be running wild
with snot-nosed joy and
screaming every word you
say with frantic excitement!
Just what
kind of messed up
childhood did you have any way?
And last
time I checked,
snot and joy do
not go together.
You're no fun.
Wait.
I think I've got it.
It's cuz' you can't
swim, isn't it?
[NAGASUMI] What,
are you kidding me?
What kind of idiot doesn't
know how to swim?
[NAGASUMI ] Help!
Please, help me!
Help, I'm drowning!
[NAGASUMI] It hurts so much.
No. I don't
wanna die.
[NAGASUMI] Mom.
Dad. Somebody.
Please.
Anybody.
Someone help me.
[DAD]
Nagasumi.
Hey!
Nagasumi!
[NAGASUMI] What the--?
Do you have any idea how long
I've been looking for you?
What the heck are you
sleeping down here for?
I was starting to think
that you'd drowned!
[NAGASUMI] Dad?
[DAD] Were you
expecting someone else?
Jeez.
[DAD] Come on, let's
head back to Grandma's.
Dad, wait!
But I did drown!
I mean, I was drowning.
And well, see,
I was really far offshore.
[DAD] Are you serious?
You were drowning and the
tide reversed and washed
you up here on the rocks?
No, there was somebody,
or maybe something, out there.
Something, you say?
[DAD] You know what it was?
You probably got
saved by a mermaid.
A mermaid?
[DAD] I was
being sarcastic, son.
You were just
dreaming. Let's go.
[DAD] I don't wanna catch
a cold on our vacation.
[NAGASUMI]
Hey! Dad!
I'm not making this up!
I really did drown!
I'm being serious here!
Hey, Dad!
C'mon!
Listen to me!
[grandmother laughs]
[GRANDMOTHER] So Nagasumi.
Ya got saved by a pretty
little mermaid, did ya?
It's true, Grandma!
I saw her!
Will you give
it a rest already?
You're embarrassing me!
How did you end up like this?
[NAGASUMI] I don't know,
but I blame my parents.
I guess there aren't any
mermaids in Saitama, are there?
That's sweet,
but you don't
have to humor him,
Grandma.
I swear to you
that I'm not making this up!
I can't count the
legends I've heard
about mermaids in
the Seto Inland Sea.
People are always claiming
to see them in these parts.
Do they really?
And ya just better hope
the legends aren't true.
Or else you're gonna be
in a whole heap of trouble.
What do you
mean by trouble?
C'mon, mom.
He was just dreaming.
I found him asleep on the beach.
It wasn't a dream!
I don't know where
he gets this stuff from.
You raised me, didn't you?
Just let me describe
her for you, okay?
She had this long,
--[SUN] Uh, hello. Good evening.
--pretty auburn hair,
--Who's this?
--and she just looked..
--It's a little late for guests,
--like a mermaid, y'know?
--isn't it?
She was actually really cute.
[NAGASUMI] Yeah!
Like this girl!
She looked like this.
[MOM]
Shut up!
Well now. There somethin'
we can do for ya, young lady?
Yes, thank you.
Well, uh, see my
name is Sun Seto.
[GRANDMOTHER] Sun Seto, huh?
--Mermaid! Mermaid...!
--So then, are you a
--friend of Nagasumi's?
--[DAD] Snap out of it!
--I'm pretty sure he doesn't
--know anybody that
here in Kagawa.
Nagasumi? That's you?
That's me.
Okay. Well.
Will you please.
Will you...
Will you please
take me as your bride!
[SUN] Please take
me as your bride!
Ya see. I
know this is kinda
sudden and you must
be surprised, but, well.
I need you to
take responsibility for
what happened between
us this afternoon.
[SUN] Responsibility
for what happened.
What do you mean?
[DAD] What the hell have you
done, you little fappy bastard?
[DAD] How could you?
And right behind your
dear ol' dad's back?
You just had to go
and make me bust
out my left hook--didn't you?
All I did was drown,
I swear!
And what does
"fappy" even mean?
That's not a real word!
[MOM] I can't believe
you'd do such a fappy thing!
You're not even
in high school yet!
What were you thinking?
--What are you talking about?
--That poor girl!
[MASA] Excuse me.
Sorry to bother so late.
[MOM AND DAD] Yakuza?
[MOM] The one in the
middle is kind of hot, though.
Honey?
[GANGSTER A] Oh, come on!
Does every housewife
think he's hot?
[GANGSTER B] I ain't getting'
in the middle of this one!
Shut your mouths
and keep 'em that way.
[GANGSTERS] Yes sir.
We're with Miss Sun.
I apologize for this
inconvenience
but I do regret to say.
That you're gonna
have to come with us.
Both of you,
Mr. and Mrs. Michishio.
[MASA] Miss Sun's
father, my boss,
is eager to meet
with the two of you.
And he's not the type
of man you keep waiting.
[MOM AND DAD] She's
a yakuza daughter!
Nooooo!!!
[MASA] I need you
to follow me now.
[GRANDMOTHER] S'just
like I said it would be.
He's in a whole heap of trouble.
[NAGASUMI] Uh, umm.
[NAGASUMI] Is there
any particular reason
you brought us
to a jagged cliff?
[MASA] All right then, everyone.
You three can go first.
[NAGASUMI]
They're trying to kill us!
The yakuza wants to kill us!
[MOM AND DAD] Nagasumi!
[NAGASUMI] Mom!
Dad!
We blame this on you!
She's dragging me down!
She's actually trying to
make sure that I'm gonna die!
[NAGASUMI] M-Mermaid!
She's the one from
this afternoon!
[GOZABURO] Hey, kid.
Wake up.
[GOZABURO] C'mon,
kid, can ya hear me?
You okay, kid?
Quick Masa!
Mouth-to-mouth!
[MASA] Yes Sir!
Breathe, dammit!
[NAGASUMI] I'm fine!
Get up! Get off!
[MOM] I know I shouldn't
be jealous of my son, but...
You do know I can
hear you, dontcha?
Don't just sit there!
Why didn't you stop him?
Oh, god, that didn't count
as my first kiss, did it?
[MOM] I wish it'd been mine.
At least don't
say it out loud.
[GOZABURO] Somethin' wrong, kid?
Ya seem pretty agitated.
So, uh, where
are we exactly?
Well, Nagasumi, we're in Sun's
house, at the bottom of the sea.
It's a house for mermaids.
[GOZABURO] Thanks for makin'
the trip all the way down here.
I'm Sun's father,
but most people know me
as the boss of the local outfit
of the Seto Fish Commision.
[GOZABURO] My name
is Gozaburo Seto.
I'm Ren Seto.
His lovely wife
and Sun's mother.
[NAGASUMI THINKS]
We're being held captive
by genuine mobsters!
How could
you do this to us?
After all we've
done for you.
Alright, enough
of the small talk,
let's just cut
to the chase here.
I brought you all down here 'cuz
my daughter saved your
son's life today.
She saved your life?
Why didn't you
tell us that?
I did!
I told you a mermaid
saved me from drowning!
[GOZABURO] Now listen close
to what I'm about to tell ya.
We live by the code
of the Mermaid law
and according to it,
any mermaid that
lets a human see
their true form...
...is sentenced
to death by execution!
[GOZABURO] We send em' off
to sleep with the fishes, see?
And there ain't nothing
we can do about it!
It has to be done!
Ain't that a pity?
Ain't that a pity my
daughter has to die?
[DAD] Uh-huh.
[NAGASUMI] Uh.
Yeah.
[MOM] Certainly.
And it's all yer
fault, ya little shit!
Why the hell should
my daughter have to
die just cuz' you don't
know how to swim? Huh?
[NAGASUMI] I don't know
how to answer that!
[REN] Now dear.
So this whole snafu
got me ta' thinkin'.
Why should a mermaid have
ta die just fer bein' seen.
[GOZABURO] When I
can solve the problem
by killing the human
who saw her instead?
--That's it!
--Don't sacrifice me!
--I'll just have you killed.
--Hell I'll kill you myself
--Boss, please calm down!
--right now you little BASTARD!
--Calm down!
You've got nothing
to worry about.
You just leave things to me.
[BOTH] 'kay.
--I'm gonna harpoon that
--This is no time for weird
--little piece of fecal matter.
--mother and son fantasies!
[GOZABURO] Let me go!
--[SUN] Knock it off, Dad!
--Let me go! He has to die!
Ya can't kill him!
I saved him so that
he wouldn't die!
[SUN] And killin' him for
no reason is just as
bad as me savin' him
according to the mob code.
But Sun....
...the code says ya have
to die fer savin' him.
Yeah, and I
can accept that!
I meant ta save his life.
It's my choice.
Go on...
Go ahead: boil me,
grill me, whatever!
[GOZABURO] How
can ya say that, Sun?
Please, just let
Daddy waste this
worthless human and
everything will be fine!
[DAD] Thanks for ruining
our vacation, Nagasumi.
[NAGASUMI] Shouldn't
you be trying to save me,
instead of blaming me?
I really do apologize.
Once my husband's blood
starts to boil,
there's no stopping him.
Uh, that's okay.
And my daughter is
typically very respectful,
but she's got this
stubborn streak about her.
Is that so?
It certainly is, Nagasumi.
We have to adhere
to the mermaid code,
but there is one
solution that doesn't
involve any of this
killing nonsense.
[GOZABURO] No!
Don't tell 'em!
Well you see, Nagasumi.
All you have to do
is marry our daughter.
Marry her?
[REN] Once you're family,
you can know Sun's true form.
It wouldn't be an issue then.
So, what do ya say?
You'll marry into the family,
won't ya handsome?
[Gozaburo growls]
[GOZABURO] Well,
Mr. and Mrs. Michishio.
[GOZABURO] I hate to
say so, but there ya have it.
[GOZABURO]
Yer unworthy son can marry
my precious, wonderful,
beautiful daughter.
He'll take her as his bride,
or we'll just have to
murder every human
that knows about us.
[GOZABURO] And that includes
the two of you as well.
As I'm sure you've
figured out by now.
Murder every human.
That includes the two of you.
You're really gonna love
being married, Nagasumi.
[MOM] I'm just overcome
with joy for you.
[NAGASUMI] Look me
in the eye and say that.
That's right.
Your parents are always
looking out for you,
and we couldn't be happier.
[NAGASUMI]Why don't you use
your left hook on him, Dad?
[MOM] He's all worn out
from using it on you earlier.
[GOZABURO] Somethin'
wrong with ya, punk?
Ya tellin' me that ya
don't think my daughter's
good enough for
you or somethin'?
I never said that!
I just don't think you
should rush us like this!
I mean, you can't force love.
We don't even
know each other yet.
There's a good chance
that she won't even...
Um, wanna marry me.
[GOZABURO]
Shut yer face, maggot!
My daughter's ready
to die and yer givin'
me this 'get to
know each other' crap?
[GOZABURO] There's no
way in hell I'll let
her marry a pathetic
piss ant like you!
I'll kill you!
You small weak fleshy--
[REN]  Now, dear!
Ya oughta respect the bravest
decision of a girl's life!
Masa! Don't you
let him get away!
[NAGASUMI] Wait!
How can you do this!
[NAGASUMI THINKS]
You gave me my first kiss.
Well, Nagasumi...
Sorry it turned out like this,
but I don't have a choice.
You'd be dead if it
weren't for her, so it only
makes sense that you
give your life for her now.
[NAGASUMI] That doesn't
make sense at all!
[GANGSTER C]
Hold it right there!
[GANGSTER D] Yahoo!
It's exterminatin' time!
[NAGASUMI] What the hell?
Why won't this door open?
[NAGASUMI] Come on!
Open dammit!
Where did that brat go?
[GANGSTER E] The water
swept him into the house.
[GOZABURO] Rip him
to shreds, Shark Fujishiro!
Shark Fujishiro?
[SHARK]
Looks like dinner time?
[NAGASUMI] Holy crap,
he's a literal shark!
[SUN] Sorry Fujishiro,
ya can't eat him.
[SHARK]
Why'd ya take my food?
Uh, wow, thank you.
You saved me again.
Sun right?
Hurry!
We'll sneak out through
the back entrance!
[NAGASUMI THINKS]
How many times am I gonna
have to be saved today?
[SUN] If you just follow
this tunnel out you'll be fine.
Come on, then!
[VOICES]
Fishy tail!
Leave this to me! 'kay.
Um, well. I don't
need to run like you do.
But doesn't it mean that
you'll have to die
if I get away?
But ya don't havta
worry 'bout that.
I am worried about it!
[NAGASUMI] Are you okay, Sun?
I'm fine, are you okay?
[NAGASUMI] Oh yeah,
I'm doing great.
I wonder if Dad's
still chasing us.
[SUN] You just called him "dad."
[NAGASUMI] No, no!
That was a slip of the tongue!
I meant to say your dad.
[SUN] But Nagasumi,
if ya take me with ya,
he'll probably hunt ya all the
way to the end of the universe.
[NAGASUMI] Good point.
Well, no matter what, we're in
a whole lot of trouble now.
Hey...
Why did you even
bother saving me when the
mermaid law says that
you're not supposed to?
Why'd I save you?
Ya see, Nagasumi.
If I saw somebody in
trouble right in front of me
and I just ignored him,
that would just disgrace
all Seto mermaids.
'Cause honor among thieves...
is honor under the seas!
[SUN] But I made this
decision on my own, ya see.
And there's no reason for
it to get you in trouble.
It's fine...
Don't you worry about me,
you just save yourself.
[GOZABURO] There ya
are, ya little maggot!
I knew I'd find ya.
Ya really think ya could
get away, you piss ant?
Take him down,
Octopus Nakajima!
[OCTOPUS]
Oc-to-py!
[NAGASUMI] He's huge!
But kind of cute.
[OCTOPUS] Murdery!
[SUN] Nagasumi!
Nice shot, Octopus.
Stop it, Dad!
[GOZABURO] I can't really
say it's been nice knowin' ya.
Not that I care, but ya
better say yer prayers.
[NAGASUMI THINKS]
No matter what.
I'll never be able to
run away from this lunatic.
No Dad!
Stop it!
Your death will save my
daughter's life,
so take it like a man!
[NAGASUMI]
Hold on!
I'd like permission to
marry your daughter sir!
[REN] Well!
[Sun gasps]
[NAGASUMI THINKS] I have
to do this for Sun.
I'll marry her, even
if it's just for show.
And then she'll be free
to make up her own mind.
Stop looking at me.
Yer makin' me blush.
There you have it, Dad.
He said it.
Ya can't kill him.
[GOZABURO] You maggot.
Think yer smart, huh?
Think ya squirmed yer
way out this one, do you?
Well you're wrong.
[GOZABURO] I'll never
let Sun marry you!
[NAGASUMI] Help me, please!
Really? You need to respect
your daughter's independence!
Will you shut up?
Any bastard that gets close to
Sun is gonna be fish food!
So I'm a dead man? Crap!
C'mon, boss,
calm down now!
[SUN] What do ya
think yer doing, Dad?
[NAGASUMI THINKS]
I spent my summer vacation
at the Seto Inland Sea.
I went swimming. I hung
out with my Grandma.
And then I wound up
taking a mermaid as my bride.
[NAGASUMI]
Please let me go, Dad!
[GOZABURO] How dare
you call me "dad"!
[SUN] Stop it, Dad!
[GOZABURO] Sink to
the bottom of the sea,
ya fappy little shit!
[SUN] Nagasumi!
♪
[NAGASUMI] Oh, man,
I can't believe I'm
engaged to such a cute girl!
And she's a mermaid!
A yakuza mermaid to boot!
Geez, what should I do?
What, I should take her on
a date to the summer festival?
Alright then, I gotta stay
cool and keep it together.
Can I do that?