Yo...
[AKENO] I apologize for not
contacting you sooner, Captain.
[CAPTAIN SWORDSMAN]
How are things progressing,
training swordsman Akeno?
[AKENO] Unfortunately,
not very well.
[AKENO] Both Seto and
Michishio refuse to break up.
And I'm starting
to think that using
the Mermaid Exam to separate
them might be impossible.
I don't recall ever telling
you this was going
to be easy, did I?
And as long as
no one's discovered
that your true goal
is to break them up,
then I'm happy.
[AKENO] Captain...
[CAPTAIN SWORDSMAN] Yes?
[AKENO] I have to
be honest with you.
With all due respect,
I'm not comfortable
with this mission.
[CAPTAIN SWORDSMAN]
You're overstepping your bounds,
training swordsman Akeno.
My apologies, Captain.
You're forgiven,
just do whatever
it takes to break
them up, got it?
It's what's best
for the both of them.
Yes.
[CAPTAIN SWORDSMAN]
This should help.
[AKENO] Is that?
[CAPTAIN SWORDSMAN] Yes.
Use it to teach Sun Seto just
how ugly human
beings really are.
[CAPTAIN SWORDSMAN]
I expect to hear from you soon.
[NARRATOR] Several dozen leagues
from the Inland Sea's foam,
Lies the land of Saitama,
birthplace and home,
But where'er you go,
the demons still roam.
A violent mob's on the scene.
Watching the
schoolboy's routine.
And poor Nagasumi
is only fourteen.
Like a stormy sea,
the course of
this love is
anything but smooth.
♪
[GOZABURO] Everybody line up!
Ya bunch 'a pathetic
little piss ants
wanna check out
Movie Land, don't ya?
[BOYS] Yeah!
Let's find the guy
who plays Kin-san,
and see how tough he really is!
[BOYS] Yeah!
[NAGASUMI] He's been
like this for the whole trip.
If he keeps this up,
he's gonna die.
Hey, Nagasumi.
Oh, hi there, Sun.
[SUN] This is where
they film all those
historical dramas
and stuff, right?
[NAGASUMI] Yep, they sure do.
[SUN] Everything
looks so authentic...
It's almost as if we're
back in the Edo Period!
Boy, I'll say!
It's like we've leapt through
time or something and--
Mawari! I'm sorry!
I need your eyes on me!
Just me!
[NAGASUMI] Look, Mom, I can fly!
You're sketchy and letchy
and you make me retchy!
Plus, you're under arrest
for forcible indecency!
You're the one
being forcible!
Nagasumi's "wrapped
up" in trouble once again.
Get it?
[SUN] Huh?
Hey, these are
really cool, gyo!
Yeah, and now
you're under arrest, gyo!
We'll buy one for
Nakajima, too, gyo!
--[AKENO] Hey...
--[AJITARO] Gyo!
[AKENO] If you
don't want to return
to Seto, then come with me.
[BURIO] So...
Miss Akeno...
What is it you
want us to do, gyo?
You will break up Nagasumi
Michishio and Sun Seto.
That's easy as pie, gyo.
[AKENO]
For your sakes, I hope so.
Additionally, the Setos and the
Edomae's must not find out.
No one can.
Do I make myself clear?
[MAGURO] Yes, ma'am, gyo.
[KAI] And if we do this...?
[KAI] You're not gonna forget
your promise, are ya?
[AKENO] No, of course I won't.
Should you succeed,
I'll nullify your failures
of the Mermaid Exam,
and you four won't get sent
back to the Inland Sea.
[KAI] Fine...
[AJITARO] We'll break
them up, ma'am.
[Fish Brothers laugh]
[MAWARI] Oh, wow!
I'm standing in front
of the most famous
center of justice from
the Edo Period!
The Court of Law!
[MAWARI] Raise your hand!
You're under oath, sir!
How do you plead?
Court is now in session!
[SUN] Mawari sure
is hyper today, huh?
She's just crazy about
historical dramas.
Well, either that or
she's just plain crazy.
[CHIMP] Nagasumi!
Get your paws off me,
you damn, dirty Chimp!
Hey, is that any
way to treat a friend?
One who comes
bearing yummy dango, too?
Not to mention cool,
refreshing soft drinks...
Why do you want
to be with me so bad?
My lord has
gone missing!
What's worse is that Akeno
has disappeared, too!
And even worse than that,
Lunar's not here either!
Team B is in ruins!
It's lonely all by myself!
Please let me join your team!
Geez, I can't even
understand what
you're saying because
of all the snot!
Yeah, I wish Lunar could
be with us, too, Chimp,
but she's real
busy workin' right now.
[NAGASUMI] That's why
she missed the field trip.
It's too bad she won't
be able to see this place.
[Lunar laughs]
Wait! That evil laugh,
it belongs to--!
We are weary of
waiting for you, Sun!
[SUN] Lunar!
What a surprise!
What are ya doin' here?
Filming a historical drama!
I re-arranged my schedule
so I could take a
break and see you guys!
But don't get
the wrong idea!
It's not like
we're here because
we wanted to have fun
with you or anything!
You are our rival
and our enemy!
[SUN] Oh, okay, but you're
still my friend, aren't ya?
That's a different issue!
Now tell me
about your dumb trip!
Lunar's as pleasant
as ever, I see.
This'd be a
great photo op!
Lunar makes time
for her school friends,
even though
she's making a movie!
[SUN] We saw the Kiyomizu
Temple, the Otowa Falls--
[LUNAR] Oh, yeah?
We had fun here!
We need to be heading
back to the set right away.
What, already?
But we barely
got to see each other.
I know. It's a
real shame, but--
Hey, I have an idea!
[KAMATA] Why don't
you come to the set
and watch us shoot the movie?
Really?
You're not shooting
on a closed set?
We are, but since
this movie's being
made by our production company,
we can be a little flexible,
what do you say, gang?
[ALL] Yeah!
Really! I've always
wanted to go behind the
scenes and see how
a movie gets made!
Then that settles it then!
Okay, everybody, this way!
[ALL] Yay!
What happened here?
A tornado maybe.
[STAFF DUDE]
Miss Lunar! Mr. Kamata!
There you are!
We weren't gone
long; what happened?
Where did all
the actors go?
To the hospital! Every
single one of them, too!
[STAFF DUDE] It was terrible!
They were attacked!
[KAMATA] What? Attacked by who?
[STAFF DUDE] This trio of masked
men who came out of nowhere!
So there's no
way we can keep
shooting since we
lost our whole cast!
Oh, no, this isn't good.
Now we're behind
schedule and over-budget.
We may miss our opening date.
Like hell we will!
This is our big movie
debut, you morons,
so we're not missing any
opening date, you hear us?
Look, I understand
how you feel, but--
But nothing!
I don't care what it takes,
go find us a cast!
Wait!
That music, it's--!
I told you I'd be back!
Papa?
[BOB] Oh, Samurai!
[MICHAEL] Bushido!
Wow, what's your
dad doing here?
He's the executive
producer of this movie.
He must have come
to terminate our problem.
Lunar!
First off, I'm adding
a million dollars
to this movie's budget!
[LUNAR PAPA] Take it!
[NAGASUMI] A million?
And secondly...
As for casting,
it's no problemo.
But how sir?
[LUNAR PAPA] Sun Seto!
And all of you humans here!
Your mission is to protect
this movie,
so you will be the actors!
[LUNAR PAPA]
Hasta la vista, babies!
Junior high students
acting in a historical drama?
That sounds completely insane!
Actually, that
sounds pretty cool!
I could become
the next Kin-san!
If I was an actor...
Chicks would dig me!
I'll marry a pop star!
Wow! It does
sound like a lot of fun!
Well, I guess I can't
be the only one who says no.
[AKENO] Count us in as well.
We'll be happy to
help out with the film.
[NAGASUMI] Akeno! And you guys.
My lord!
You've returned!
I missed you so much!
[KAI] Oh, how I've missed
your groveling, Chimp!
This is really exciting.
I'm a big fan of
historical dramas.
Yeah, so are the Branchial
Respiration Three!
We love 'em, too, gyo!
[FISH BROTHERS]
Gyo, gyo, gyo, gyo...
Then there's
no time to waste!
Let's get to wardrobe
and into costume!
Yeah!
I still don't
know about this.
[LUNAR] Down the hall there's a
changing room
for the girls to use.
Boys, change wherever. Alright?
Right!
Hey, hold on a second...
Where's Akeno?
I don't know. She was
with us just a minute ago.
[KAI] Hey, everybody!
[KAI] I got a surprise!
Yeah, what?
[KAI] Soft drinks for everybody!
[NAGASUMI] Soft drinks?
They're nice and cold, too!
Thanks, that was
really thoughtful!
And just as I was
getting thirsty, too!
Well, let's drink 'em
while they're cold!
Aren't you guys gonna
have any soda?
Oh , uh, we already
drank ours, gyo.
[KAI] It's too much
trouble with this thing on.
[NAGASUMI THINKS] The last
time I had a mermaid drink,
things didn't go too well.
I'll skip it and the side
effects, thank you.
[MAWARI] That was good!
[LUNAR] Okay, girls!
Let's get changed!
Sure thing!
You lead the way!
[LUNAR] Not you, perv!
[Fish Brothers laugh]
[AKENO] I see.
[AKENO] So it went well?
[MAGURO]
Yes, of course it did, gyo.
Miss Akeno, ma'am.
What good could one
little soft drink do, gyo?
[AKENO] What you gave
them wasn't a soft drink,
but a secret potion passed
down among we merfolk.
The Fish Shot!
Fish Shot?
[AKENO] It's a powerful
potion that releases
the inner desires
of those who drink it.
After just one little sip,
you can no longer
hide your heart's
hidden desires,
and you're transformed
into a raving,
single-minded beast who
acts solely on instinct.
[AKENO] When Sun
sees how everyone
acts after drinking it,
she'll become disillusioned
with the human race,
hence the use of the Fish Shot.
I didn't want to take
such cowardly measures,
but I have no choice
but to follow my orders.
Well then... I've probably said
more than I needed to.
Boy...
All this explaining's
made me fairly parched.
[AJITARO] Try one of
these; it's refreshing.
I will, thank you.
What do you
mean "refreshing?"
This is the Fish Shot!
[BURIO] Oh...
[AJITARO] It...
[MAGURO] Is?
[AKENO] Please don't
tell me you guys--
We drank it, gyo!
It was good, gyo!
Smooth and full of flavor gyo!
[AKENO] You imbeciles!
How are we supposed to do our
job if we're hopped
up on this stuff?
[NAGASUMI] So I guess
we're just supposed
to hang out here
until filming starts, huh?
I've been pretty nervous
since I left wardrobe.
Speaking of which, you're not
wearing THAT
in the movie, are you?
[KAI] My full dress uniform?
What's the problem?
Spacesuits weren't
around in the Edo Period.
[KAI] Would ya
just chill out?
[KAI] That reminds me, did ya
drink the drink I brought ya?
Yep, it was tasty.
[KAI] Glad ya liked it.
[NAGASUMI THINKS] Actually, I
didn't. I didn't drink a drop!
[NAGASUMI] I know
it's a historical drama,
but do you know what
this movie's about?
I haven't seen a script.
[KAI] How dumb are ya?
Didn't ya see the sign outside?
[KAI] The one that
says "Ikeda Inn" on it?
[NAGASUMI] Is the Ikeda
Inn famous or something?
[KAI] Dammit, you are ignorant!
Alright, listen up
and let me explain!
On July 8th, 1864--
[fast forward tape sound]
[KAI] So? Didja
learn something?
Yep!
Am I imagining things
or is someone spying on us?
[KAI] Hah... Maybe the
Shinsengumi's on your tail.
[KAI] You believe in
mermaid-human marriage
which sort of makes
you like the Ishin Shishi
rebels the Shinsengumi
attacked at the Inn...
Wait, maybe attacked's
not the right word.
Massacred's more like it.
[AKENO] End of the line, rebel!
[AKENO] Nagasumi Michishio,
you scoundrel who
dares do harm to
the ruling government.
We, the Shinsengumi have
come for your punishment!
[AKENO] My Kotetsu sword
is thirsting for your blood.
Wow. That costume looks
fantastic on you Akeno,
and that prop
sword almost looks real!
[AKENO] Hmm...
I suppose the blade was dull.
It feels pretty real, too!
I think I'm needed on the set!
[KAI] I got 'em!
What the--?
Stop Kai! Lemme go!
[KAI] Don't worry, Miss Akeno!
He's not going anywhere!
Take 'em out!
What's going on here?
The world outside
is dark and cold,
but you, you're just like a big,
bright ray of sunshine
beaming down on us all!
[AKENO] Give me your
warmth, I command you!
[CAPTAIN SWORDSMAN]
I hope you're following
my orders to the letter, Akeno.
[CAPTAIN SWORDSMAN]
You've got it together for
someone your age, but you
can be clumsy sometimes.
I just hope you've got
everything under
control right now.
[people crying out]
[KAI] N-Not again!
[KAI] My eyes! My eyes!
My beautiful, gorgeous eyes!
Nagasumi Michishio!
Come give me a hug right now!
A-Akeno?
[NAGASUMI] She's gonna kill me!
And Michishio?
[AKENO] Hey, what do
you know! Look who's here!
You've got perfect
timing, Captain!
[CAPTAIN SWORDSMAN] Don't
talk to me in public, you idiot!
Aye aye, sir!
Captain, my Kotetsu's
broken, so I humbly
request permission to
draw the Morning Star!
Hold up. Why are you
acting so strangely?
[AKENO] Huh?
Why, whatever would make
you think that
about me, Captain?
[AKENO] Thanks for
giving me permission
to draw the Morning Star,
sir! See ya!
[CAPTAIN SWORDSMAN]
But I never did!
Maybe she gave up.
[NAGASUMI]
What the heck was that for?
[Lunar giggles]
[NAGASUMI] Lunar?
What are you doing--!
[LUNAR] We re-arranged
our shooting schedule
for one reason
and one reason only,
so that we could
see you, Nagasumi.
So what is she doing here?
[NAGASUMI] Wait, what
are you talking about?
[LUNAR] We don't
see you for days,
and when we finally do,
you flirt and play hard-to-get
with her on our set.
[LUNAR] You've got
some nerve... You...
[LUNAR] Freakin' manservant!
Sun was bad enough,
but now you've taken
up with Akeno, too?
You gigolo! You player!
You lousy two-timer!
We're going to make
it so that every girl
knows you're mine,
and the way to do
that is with a love
scene captured on film.
[NAGASUMI] No! No one'll
want to marry me then!
It'll be good
for our movie, too.
After all, viewers
aren't satisfied these
days unless a movie has
at least one love scene in it.
[NAGASUMI] But that's
only with R-rated movies!
[LUNAR] You're gonna
marry me on camera,
and every marriage
begins with a kiss!
[MAWARI] I may not
know the ABCs of love,
but I know the stench of
evil whenever I smell it!
[MAWARI] I've got law
enforcement in my blood,
and when I see someone
committing a crime,
I teach them the
rules of this society!
[MAWARI]
They call me the demonic
Disciplinary Committee
member of Isono Eighth.
Mawari Zenigata!
And I'm not gonna let
you slide, Nagasumi Michishio!
About what?
You've trampled
on the emotions
of several young women, pal!
Sadly, the courts don't
consider that a crime.
So the law won't punish you.
But I will!
[MAWARI] How 'bout
telling me what you
meant by those things
you said last night?
[NAGASUMI] Uh, no thanks!
[NAGASUMI] Now what?
Say it now.
My name! Say it!
You heard me! Say my name!
It's Class Rep.
Uh huh, Class Rep.
Yeah, It's Class
Rep, isn't it?
[VOICES] Is that
your final answer?
[CLASS REP] Yes, it is I,
the wallflower who's
always seen, but rarely heard;
the one who's
so easily forgotten.
[CLASS REP] But not anymore!
I bet you won't forget
me now, will ya?
Not with those
throwing stars, I won't!
[NAGASUMI] I don't know
what's going on with them,
but I gotta get away
from these crazy girls!
[AKENO] Nagasumi!
You might be able
to run, but you can't hide.
[NAGASUMI]
Oh, crap! I'm cut off!
[BURIO] To protect the
order in the capitol...
[AJITARO] All Ishin Shishi
rebels must be killed!
[MAGURO] That task falls to us:
the most handsome
samurai in Kyoto.
[BURIO] Toshizo Burikata!
[AJITARO] Soji Ajita!
[MAGURO] Hajime Maguto!
The Branchial Respiration
Shinsengumi has arrived!
[NAGASUMI] Arrived to do what?
To help you meet your maker,
Nagasumi Michishio, gyo!
[NAGASUMI] Did you know
your name's spelled wrong?
[AJITARO] Shut up!
[MAGURO]
Gatotsu technique, my brothers!
[NAGASUMI] Gatotsu!
[AKENO] Squeeze
me like a grapefruit!
Hug me dammit!
[AKENO] I said squeeze!
Not you, you mangy beast!
Get your paws off me!
[NAGASUMI] Hey, stop that.
[BURIO] Look, it's him!
[AJITARO] I don't believe it!
Movie Land's beloved mascot!
[MAGURO] Yay,
it's Sarumage, gyo!
[BURIO] If he jumps on you,
something good'll happen gyo!
[AKENO] Like hell
it will, you moron!
[AKENO] Stop or
Nagasumi'll get away!
[NAGASUMI] See ya!
[MAGURO] Too late, gyo!
[BURIO] After him, gyo!
[NAGASUMI] Thanks
a lot, Sarumage!
I hope you got a handful!
[CHIMP] Did I ever!
You filthy beast!
[NAGASUMI] Why's
everyone acting so weird?
[NAGASUMI] Wait a minute?
Could it have been those drinks?
[Lunar chuckles]
[LUNAR] Come here, manservant.
[MAWARI] You're
under arrest, meow!
[CLASS REP]
My name. Say my name!
[AKENO] I'm so cold!
How vexing! Nagasumi,
give me your warmth!
I'm surrounded!
[NAGASUMI] Oh, man,
this looks like the end!
[SUN] Hey, what's goin' on here?
What're ya guys
doin' to Nagasumi?
[NAGASUMI] Sun!
If you want 'em,
get in line. 'Kay?
[SUN] I won't let anyone
pick on Nagasumi.
[SUN] That's what
ya did, so all of
ya are gonna answer to me.
Please Sun, wait!
Ya see because,
"honor among thieves" is
"honor under the seas!"
Ya hear?
[Akeno rages]
[AKENO] Nagasumi!
You're not going to give me
any warmth, are you, you bum?
Akeno, you apologize right
now to him for saying that!
[AKENO] Never!
[AKENO] And as for you!
[AKENO] Say hello
to the sacred weapon
bestowed upon my family
by the God of Heaven:
the Tuning Sword "Morning Star!"
Too bad for you ultrasonic
waves don't work on it!
Is that so?
Well, if ya don't intend
to apologize at all,
then the only one who's gonna be
doin' any cuttin'
around here is me!
[AKENO] Bring it on, baby,
and while you're at it,
hug me and squeeze me
and hug me and squeeze me!
[CAPTAIN SWORDSMAN] Enough!
[AKENO] Of what?
[SUN] Who are you?
This is insane.
I expected some
challenges, but THIS...
[CAPTAIN SWORDSMAN] This
is a total freaking nightmare!
[CAPTAIN SWORDSMAN]
The Fish Shot brings out
the hidden desires in people.
So what you're telling me is
that even after
drinking it, Sun Seto...
[AKENO] Yes...
She's still protecting
Nagasumi above everything else.
So all you did was
discover her true desire.
Well, we're back
to square one it seems.
Breaking them up might
be impossible, Captain.
If you ask me.
[CAPTAIN SWORDSMAN]
Training swordsman Akeno...
...you're to continue
monitoring those
two as a Mermaid
Exam administrator.
Understood?
[AKENO] Yes...
I understand, Captain.
You have to atone
for this blunder
and the only
way to do that is by
carrying your mission
through to the end.
So do it right this time.
[AKENO] Yes, sir.
[SUN] Nagasumi,
over here! Hurry!
[NAGASUMI] Sun, wait!
What's going on?
[SUN] Just follow me,
quick! Come on!
See there?
[NAGASUMI] Wow.
A full moon.
Pretty, isn't it?
The minute I saw it I
knew I wanted to share
it with ya alone
and with nobody else.
But do ya wanna know why?
Cause on this trip,
we haven't had a chance
to have a special
moment together.
Oh, Sun...
You're the best.
[NAGASUMI] These
last couple of days
have been pretty rough on me.
But you know what?
Seeing this with you
now makes it all worth it.
♪
[VOICES] Masa Today!
Been awhile, hasn't it...?
You haven't come
to visit in quite some time.
[MASA] Oh, you know.
This and that...
Were you worried about me?
Not really.
[door opens and closes
with chimes ringing]
[PROPRIETRESS]
Hello and welcome.
[MASA] I've gotta admit, I'm
impressed you found this place.
I never expected
to see you here.
[MASA] I suppose you
just got off work, huh?
Well, in that case, let's do
some nice, relaxing drinking.
[MASA] Owner... Let's have one
of the usual if you don't mind.
Sure...
[MASA] You'll like that.
It's "The Sad Father,"
a house specialty.
It's slightly bitter,
but I think you'll find
it takes the edge off.
[MASA] I can tell you're upset,
but this is all a big
misunderstanding.
You're wife and I--
Just give her back.
I've told you, there's
nothing going on man.
Don't lie to me!
I've seen how she looks at you!
It's only a matter of time
before she leaves me!
You're just imagining
things, pal.
You're the only one
who understands me, kitty.
You'll never leave me, right?
[MASA] Let's get really
sauced tonight, okay?
Don't worry...
I'll stay by your side
until you pass out.
[DAD] You will?
You're a great guy.
[MASA] None of
the either please!
[DAD] But give me back my wife!
[MASA] Whoa, whoa! And
none of that either, please.
[NAGASUMI] A harsh
reality confronts us
when we return
from our field trip.
Behold, a story of families
who seek and are hurt by love!
As a father and a man,
there things one must do!
Next time, the
definitive edition of this
Saitama Noir comes to you
in slow-mo, high-speed imaging!
I've never seen
such amazing papas!