[NARRATOR (SHARK)]
The beast approaches.
Silently, it stalks its prey,
with golden eyes
that pierce the night.
[panicked breathing]
[MAKI THINKS] It's gettin'
closer. It's comin' for me!
No!
[NARRATOR] Several dozen leagues
from the Inland Sea's foam,
Lies the land of Saitama,
birthplace and home.
But where'er you go,
the demons still roam.
A violent mob's on the scene.
Watching the
schoolboy's routine.
And poor Nagasumi
is only fourteen.
Like a stormy sea, the course of
this love is
anything but smooth.
♪
[LUNAR] We'll take that!
Hey, what're you doing?
You can't just help
yourself to my plate!
I was saving that for last!
Whatever...
You should be
happy that's all we took.
What's yours is
ours, manservant,
and don't you ever forget it.
[NAGASUMI] Yeah,
well maybe I spit on
that when you weren't looking!
What do you think
about that, huh?
[LUNAR] Ew! That's gross!
Don't even joke about that!
Somewhere along the line,
this became my seat.
It's okay.
Here, Nagasumi,
ya' can have mine.
Wow, Sun.
[LUNAR] We'll take that, too!
[Lunar laughs]
[DAD] Dear... Would you
get me some more, please?
I swear, you kids
are hopeless!
There's plenty of food left,
so no more fighting, 'kay?
[ALL] 'kay!
[NAGASUMI] Do you
want some ketchup, Sun?
[SUN] Sure,
I'll try a little bit.
[LUNAR] Hey, what about us?
Maybe we want some!
Um, Dear?
There! See?
Plenty for everyone!
[SUN] Wait--aren't we
forgettin' someone?
I haven't seen
Maki all mornin'.
What about me?
Doesn't anyone notice
that I'm missing?
[LUNAR] Huh? What do you mean?
[MOM] Dear, you've
been over there
mumbling to yourself
this whole time.
Honestly.
So. I've become
nothing but a bit
player in my own home.
No!
That sounded
like Maki, didn't it?
[Maki crying]
[Nagasumi laughs]
[NAGASUMI]
Looks like Maki finally
met her match, huh?
Don't just stand there,
ya damn sea louse!
Get this thing offa me!
Aww. It's okay.
It's just a little kitty.
See? Cute, huh?
[NAGASUMI] Um...
So now what's
wrong with you two?
Don't tell me,
you're scared of kittens?
C'mon, relax!
It's just a tiny little thing,
it can't hurt you!
There's really nothing
to be afraid of!
We are not afraid of it!
You really think
a super star like us
would be scared of such
a puny little creature?
Ridiculous!
[NAGASUMI] Here.
[kitty purrs]
[MAKI] It's tastin' us!
It's tastin' us!
I'd say that's
pretty scared.
[LUNAR] Well just
what do you expect?
We're mermaids after all!
That kitty's
our natural enemy!
To it we're food!
So then, does that mean all sea
people are scared of cats?
[MAKI] P- Pretty much.
[CLASS REP] Aw, too cute!
Yeah, right?
It just started following
me this morning.
I guess it likes me!
So what? Cute or not,
you're still not allowed
to bring animals
to school with you!
Maybe you need some
lessons on the rules of this--
[kitty meows]
[VOICES] We knew it!
'Course, it wouldn't be right to
just abandon it, either,
so now that it's here,
I guess we're
left with no choice
but to take it into custody
until school's out.
Yeah! We have to!
[MAWARI] Then I'd
better hold it for now.
I may not look it,
but I am a fully
trained and certified
cat handler!
Wow, that cat
sure is popular.
Everyone loves it.
[LUNAR] This is
completely unacceptable!
How could some
mangy, savage beast
get more attention than us?
We're the star here!
[MAKI THINKS]
That damn sea louse!
What is he tryin' to pull,
bringin' that freakin'
thing to school?
[NAGASUMI] Hey, Mikawa!
Oh, Chimp.
You beckoned
for me, my lord?
Mirror mirror on the wall
who's the handsomest of 'em all?
Why, you are, my lord.
I see.
And remind me:
who's the richest
of 'em all? Huh?
That's you as
well, my lord.
So tell me--who'd
make the most
perfect husband
for Sun of 'em all?
Clearly.
You would my lord!
Quite...
Oh, Nagasumi Michishio!
I didn't see you there.
[NAGASUMI] I'm
pretty sure you did.
[NAGASUMI] Anyway!
[kitty meows]
I want you to meet
my new friend!
Pretty cute, huh?
Yeah sure. Real cute.
The power!
[NAGASUMI THINKS]
Mermaids can't deal with cats.
They completely freak out!
Which means the next
time I see Sun's dad...
[Nagasumi laughs]
[MASA] What are you
doing there, Nagasumi?
Oh! Hi Masa!
Aw it's a kitten.
Those innocent eyes
just melt the heart.
[NAGASUMI] Huh?
Wait, Masa--you mean
you're not scared of cats?
Well, I used to be.
When I was a kid I was scared
out of my mind by them.
[MASA] But now...
I wouldn't
say I like them, but...
[NAGASUMI THINKS]
Masa as a kid, wow.
[MASA] Looking back,
it almost seems silly,
but we all have our share
of childhood fears, right?
And in time, we eventually
outgrow them.
He's so wise.
[MASA] Well,
if you'll excuse me,
I have to go prepare for class.
So then,
guess this mermaid
fear of cats isn't
as bad as I thought
if adults can outgrow it.
Damn, and I had
such big plans, too.
It would'a been fun to see
Sun's dad runnin'
scared for a change.
[GOZABURO]
What was that, maggot?
Somethin' 'bout puttin'
the scare inta' me, huh?
Yeah, let's see
ya try it, piss ant!
[NAGASUMI] No.
I wouldn't ever think that--
Huh? Hey what's
that'cha got there?
Nothing! It's nothing!
Let's see it.
[kitty meows]
[Gozaburo screams]
[NAGASUMI]
It's just a cat.
[GOZABURO]
You're a bad boy, bringin'
a wild animal
to school, Nagasumi.
[NAGASUMI] Sorry.
You wanna confiscate it?
[GOZABURO]
Nah, no need for that.
[NAGASUMI] But teacher!
It's against the rules!
You should really take it!
[Nagasumi laughs]
So, as it turns out--
Sun's dad's still
terrified of kittens!
What? Mr. Seto? Really?
Hard to believe,
what with his "tough guy"
exterior and all.
Don't judge a
book by its cover.
[SUN] Nagasumi?
Oh, Sun! Come
on over, it's okay.
I promise I won't
let go of the cat.
Ya know.... Nagasumi,
I wish ya wouldn't
be so hard on Dad.
There's a real good reason
why he's still scared of cats.
There is?
[SUN] Yeah...
It's 'cause of somethin' that
happened when he was a kid.
Your dad as a kid.
That's hard to imagine.
[SUN] He told me he
was takin' a nap one day,
mindin' his own business,
when a cat came along.
[SUN] And it bit him on the ear!
And then his ear
got infected and
almost fell off,
or somethin'.
He's had a bad case
of cat-phobia ever since.
[NAGASUMI] Oh...
Alright! Everybody! Get to
yer seats. We're startin'.
[NAGASUMI] Well,
speak of the devil.
[NAGASUMI THINKS]
H-He's looking at me like
he wants to eat me alive!
Any other day, this would
be my cue to run for it.
[NAGASUMI] But today--
I've got this little guy.
[kitty meows]
[GOZABURO] I'm the boss!
I never retreat! I never beg!
And I never look back!
What's wrong, boss?
Someone need whackin'?
[GOZABURO] Dammit.
The maggot's gone'n pissed
me off for the last time.
So this time, oh,
he'll see exactly what happens,
when you mess with me.
Let me do it!
I've just been
waitin' for an excuse
to teach that damn
sea louse a lesson!
Good. I'm callin' in my
elite guard to back ya' up.
But, boss...!
Using the elite guard?
Isn't that--?
[GOZABURO] Overkill.
An' they're all yours.
[GOZABURO] That
little shit thinks he's
a big man now, does he?
Thinks he can push me around?
Well if that's the game
he wants to play, fine!
Let's play!
It's my turn now--an'
I'm about to start pushin' back!
[SHARK] Listen up?
We have some
new students with us?
They're on temporary transfer
from Seto Junior High?
And starting immediately they'll
be joining the boys' gym class?
Transfer students
from Seto, huh?
I wanna do a
temporary transfer to
the girls' gym class
for the day! Can I?
[NAGASUMI] Shut it.
Before we get started,
come introduce yourselves?
I'm Maguro, here from
Seto Junior High, gyo.
I'm Ajitaro, gyo.
I'm Burio, gyo.
[ALL] We hope we can
all be great friends, gyo!
[BURIO] My name is Burio, gyo!
I'm a master of surprise
tactics and disguise, gyo!
Only a brilliant
strategist like me can lead
this crack squad of
battle-hardened commandos!
Never say die, gyo!
I'm Ajitaro, gyo!
I'm a whiz at
information gathering!
Using internet auctions,
I can get you anything at all,
from limited-edition DVD's
to collectible figurines, gyo!
[MAGURO] And last
but not least...
I'm Maguro, gyo!
My red flesh is
light yet flavorful,
making me a popular
guy at dinnertime,
perfect for sushi
and sashimi, gyo!
But please, just don't
overfish me, okay?
[BURIO] Together--we
scare the tears
right out of crying children!
We are the elusive elite guard
of Gozaburo Seto himself!
We are--!
The Branchial
Respiration Brothers!
[MAGURO] What sort of
trouble will we stir up next?
Tune in to find out!
Everybody, let's give
them a warm welcome, okay?
[NAGASUMI THINKS] These
guys are definitely merfolk!
What are they after?
Attention?
Anyway, they suck big
time at looking like humans!
Today we'll be playing
a friendly soccer match?
We'll split into two teams,
White and Red?
Gyo, gyo, gyo...
Seriously man, can't you
do something about that outfit?
[KAI] How am I s'posed
ta endure a bright,
wide-open place
without this?
How 'bout you just stick
to the sidelines on this one.
[KAI] You wish!
Anything you can do,
I can do ten times as well!
[Kai laughs]
[SHARK] And begin?
Is this what
you wanted, Maki?
Yeah!
We'll take advantage
of the confusion
of the game to give that
worthless sea louse a poundin'!
Quite the perfect plan,
if I do say so myself!
Try not to screw
this up, you three!
You! Quickly,
which one of these
boys is Nagasumi Michishio, gyo?
There. That's him.
[Kai still laughing]
[MAGURO] Take that you!
How dare you torment
the boss with a cat, gyo?
[KAI] You three obviously got
death wishes, kickin' me!
[AJITARO] Can it,
you NASA wannabe!
Those morons.
If the boss wanted
him worked over,
then why didn't he just have
me beat up the tasty human?
[MAKI] 'Cause you'd
eat him, Fujishiro.
That's a bad thing?
[MAKI] Miss Sun would
prob'ly say so, yeah.
[KAI] That's it!
I'll fillet every
last one of ya!
Get back here!
Wow... you sure
were right Mikawa.
You got your butt kicked ten
times better than I would've.
[GIRL] Boy, I'm hungry!
[GOZABURO] You dipshits!
[glass breaks]
I can't believe you
clobbered the wrong guy!
Now go back out there and
freakin' cream the right maggot!
We, we're real sorry,
Boss! (gyo)
Maki! This time you're leadin'
the attack personally!
[MAKI] On it! C'mon boys!
Let's go kick some ass!
[ALL] Gyo!
Right. That's the
sea louse, there.
Get ready.
[BURIO] Hey hey hey!
[MAGURO] You hold
it right there, gyo!
Yeah, ya stinkin'
shriveled up sardine!
[kitty meows]
[ALL]
Oh crap.
[kitty meows]
What the hell're you doin'?
You're s'posed to be "elite"!
But, we're
too scared! Gyo.
Then what the heck
did the Boss call ya in for?
Get yer worthless butts
over there and do somethin'!
But just listen
to that thing!
[kitty meows]
[AJITARO]
That bloodthirsty roar.
It sounds like it's
royally pissed off, gyo!
Is it daring us to
come over there?
It's like the grim reaper,
reaching out for us.
[ALL]
What a terrifying monster, gyo!
Okay, do
rock-paper-scissors
to see who's goin' out there!
Are you crazy? We can't!
That's suicide!
If we don't show
him what the
Seto outfit is made
of here an' now,
he'll be tormentin'
us like this forever!
[MAKI] Now do it!
On the count of three!
[ALL]
Rock, paper, scissors!
[NAGASUMI] What the
heck are they doing?
[NAGASUMI] Oops! Hey!
[kitty meows]
[ALL]
The monster's been released!
Run for your lives!
'Kay. Let's take a
peek at how they're doin'.
[MAKI] Boss! Run for it!
[GOZABURO] Ah! It's a
furry saber-toothed dragon!
[GOZABURO] Aahh! It's
a furry saber-toothed dragon!
[CAT] Roar!
[ALL] Ah!
Run away!
[kitty meows]
[ALL] Ah!
Run away!
Wait! You're those three
idiots from gym class!
[kitty meows]
[MAGURO] Tuna!
[BURIO]
Maguro's been captured, gyo!
Maguro! Maguro!
Burio! Stop! Gyo! He's gone!
You can't help him!
[NAGASUMI] Now hold on,
everyone, let's calm down here.
I'll just get the cat and then--
Yeah ya morons!
Calm tha' hell down!
At times like this!
a gotta stay calm!
An' call the
local fire department!
[GOZABURO] Just like this.
[fire alarm bell]
[FIREMAN] Fire outbreak!
Fire outbreak!
[FIREMAN] The location is
Isono Eighth Junior High School.
[FIREMAN] Isono Fire
Department, mobilize all units!
Emergency! Emergency!
Send reinforcements immediately!
This is an emergency
dispatch request!
[CREW MEMBER]
Urgent orders to all ships
in the Pacific region.
Emergency. Code red. Code red.
Stand by for takeoff.
This is not a drill.
I repeat, this is not a drill.
Strategic target:
Isono Eighth Junior High School.
[ANNOUNCER] All students,
follow your teacher's
orders and evacuate the
building in an orderly fashion.
Please, no running or pushing.
C'mon, you heard him!
Nobody panic!
Follow the rules!
[CLASS REP] Please
everybody, form a line,
and walk to the
courtyard, single file!
[MAKI] Whoa! It's too late!
Everybody's
already freakin' out!
[kitty meows]
[FIREMAN] Please,
don't try to go inside.
It's too dangerous.
Maguro, gyo!
Maguro's in there!
Let me go, gyo!
[MAGURO] Boss. Save yourself.
It's all over for me.
I'm sorry that I failed ya.
Pull yourself together!
I just wish
I could've seen the,
the blue waters of the sea.
[GOZABURO] This.
This can't be happenin'!
Maguro. Maguro!
[GOZABURO] Dammit
where's that fire department!
Paramedics! Anybody!
Calm down.
I've caught the kittie.
Dear!
[GOZABURO] Ah my head!
[REN] What the hell
were you thinkin'?
Seriously, you're
supposed to be men!
[MASA] We're so sorry. So sorry.
How about you try acting
like it for a change
No worries. I'm just
glad it was a false alarm.
[SUN] Sheesh, that turned
into a real mess, huh?
So, Nagasumi,
did you learn your lesson?
Yeah. I guess bringing
a kitten to school
probably wasn't the brightest
idea that I've ever had.
But, it was kinda fun
having your dad on
the run from me, even if
it was just for one day.
Oh, Nagasumi, you haven't
learned a thing at all have you?
No, I guess not.
[GOZABURO] Didja hear that?
If we let this slide,
he'll keep walkin'
all over us every
chance he gets!
This is our
last chance boys!
We'll show 'em, we ain't
about to lose to some damn cat!
Let's go over there and show 'em
what the Seto gang is made of!
Gyo! Gyo!
Right! Then we're stickin'
to the plan! Burio! Go.
[BURIO] Oh, dear!
[BURIO] My heart! I have
a sharp pain in my chest!
Please. Someone! Help me!
[SUN] Burio, uh?
What're ya doin'
out here, wearin' a skirt?
[BURIO THINKS] Busted!
Damn, but that's
my daughter for ya...
too smart to
fall for some disguise!
Don't give up, gyo!
Hang in there, gyo!
[BURIO] You must
have me confused
with some other yellowtail.
I'm just a frail maiden, gyo!
Yeah, right.
Give it up, Burio.
[BURIO] No... I'm not him!
I'm Burittney! Gyo.
Yeah! Nice save!
Alright. Whatever.
So tell us what's
wrong, Burittney.
Oh. I'm having
sharp chest pains.
Everything's
going to be okay.
[NAGASUMI] I can't believe
I'm going along with this.
[kitty meows]
[NAGASUMI] What are
you doing, you jerk?
[kitty meows]
Burio!
That was brilliant!
You mean, Burittney!
It's only natural that
we merfolk can't
win against a feline
while it's on dry land.
But drop it in the water,
and that pathetic swimmer
is certainly no match for us!
Hear that, maggot?
We're not afraid
of no stinkin' cat!
You got it?
[kitty crying out]
Nagasumi!
[NAGASUMI] THINKS I'm the
one who's responsible for this,
since I'm the one who
brought the cat to school.
So.
Sun? Why?
The underwater
stuff's my job, remember?
[NAGASUMI] Wait! Sun!
What are you doing?
That thing's a cat!
[SUN] No, don't struggle!
I can't save ya' that way!
[SUN] Maki!
[MAKI] I'd be just as
happy lettin' you drown!
But I always pay back my debts!
Do you hear me?
That's what our honor
among thieves is all about!
[Maki cries out]
Cat. Scary. Cat.
[SUN] Maki?
Thanks for helpin.
Aw, Miss Sun.
It was nothin', really!
[NAGASUMI] Sun!
Here, you can
give me the cat,
I'll take it from you!
No, it's alright.
Are you sure,
'cause I thought...
I thought you
were afraid of cats.
[Sun laughs]
I get worried and
come check on things,
and this is what I find?
[REN] You imbeciles didn't get
enough back at the school, huh?
Soon as I get here, I have to
teach you another lesson!
Just so you know,
this behavior is
why ya' can never get
over your cat phobia!
You damn moron!
It takes one
to know one.
But look at those
kids on the other hand...
They seem to have
a pretty good vibe going.
[SUN] Ow!
[NARRATOR (SHARK)]
The beast approaches.
Silently, it stalks its prey,
with golden eyes
that pierce the night.
Wow, it's really
great the way
Maki's getting
along with the cat now,
don't you think so, ladies?
[SUN] Yeah. Great.
It's eating me!
Get it off!
[MAKI] Sea louse!
♪
[NAGASUMI]
Looking back, it's just been one
fight after another for me
since that day this summer.
Maybe I should
reconsider things.
I mean, was this supposed
to be a battle show?
No!
So let's go back to it being
a sweet, innocent love story!
Okay? Time for a date with Sun!
But the minute
I think that, you appear.
Who are you,
beautiful girl in glasses?