[AKENO] Who are you supposed
to be? I don't have all night!
[BURIO] Hmph! If you wanna
know that badly, I'll tell you.
I'm Burio the Flash!
I'm Ajitaro the Resourceful!
I'm Maguro in Season!
[DYNAMITE GINJI] And I'm--!
[alert]
[OCTOPUS NAKAJIMA] Octopy!
[ALL] We're Isono Eight's
shot-caller group!
We rule the school's gangs!
[OCTOPUS NAKAJIMA] Octopy!
[AKENO] Like hell you do!
I already told you bums
that you failed the test,
so just shut up and stand down
until I tell you otherwise!
[OCTOPUS NAKAJIMA] Octopy!
[BURIO] Shut up! We don't
take orders from no one!
We're the shot-callers, gyo!
Right, Mr. Nakajima?
[OCTOPUS NAKAJIMA] Octopy!
[MAGURO] Now you've done it!
Sounds like you've
pissed Mr. Nakajima off, gyo!
[OCTOPUS NAKAJIMA] Octopy!
Let's teach her a lesson and
show her who runs
things around here!
Well, whaddaya say,
Mr. Nakajima?
Leave this challenger
to us, Mr. Nakajima!
[ALL] Die, Vexingly Sexy
Shot-Caller!
[OCTOPUS NAKAJIMA] Octopy!
[BURIO] Whoa. She's tough.
[AKENO] I knew you were
small fries from the fact
that you teamed up.
Even together, you're powerless.
[NARRATOR] Akeno Shiranui
is an administrator
of the Mermaid Exam.
Being the toughest person
at Isono Eighth Junior High,
she's considered to
be the Shot-Caller,
a position she
neither wants nor claims,
but one that will
cause a crisis.
[AKENO] How vexing.
[NARRATOR] Several dozen leagues
from the Inland Sea's foam,
Lies the land of Saitama,
birthplace and home,
But where'er you go,
the demons still roam.
A violent mob's on the scene.
Watching the
schoolboy's routine.
And poor Nagasumi
is only fourteen.
Like a stormy sea, the course of
this love is
anything but smooth.
♪
Hey!
What is your
desire, Miss Akeno?
Why are you dogging
me so early in the morning?
To settle the score?
No, no! Not at all! Please,
you've got it all wrong,
Ms. Akeno, gyo!
One at a time!
It's because
we can't let anything
happen to you,
our Boss of Bosses!
[AKENO] Something's fishy.
Did Gozaburo Seto send you?
We came on
our own, ma'am!
Your strength
won us over!
We're thrilla-thrilla-thrilled
by it, gyo!
[AJITARO USING MASA'S VOICE]
It's like the old saying,
"Yesterday's rivals are
tomorrow's friends."
Wow, Ajitaro, you sounded
just like Masa then!
You really think so?
[NARRATOR] Masa is
the idol they look up to.
[GIRL A] So Akeno's
the Shot-Caller now?
[GIRL B] They called
her "Boss of Bosses!"
[BOY A] Scary!
You're annoying! Beat it!
How very vexing.
[BURIO] You're the
toughest one in school!
[AJITARO] And the
most intimidating!
[AKENO] Would you
shut up, you imbeciles?
You too? Why are
you joining them?
Well, ya see, it just
seemed so lively over here!
Hi, Akeno...
Quite the gathering
you've gotgoing on.
Everyone seems so excited.
Annoying is
more like it. Huh?
[AKENO] What are
you doing, you pervert?
Please feel free
to call me "Chimp,"
oh Boss of Bosses.
[AKENO] I'm going
to call you "dead"
unless you tell me
what you're doing!
I only pledge my loyalty
to the most powerful.
Therefore I pledge
to serve you
twenty-four seven as
your humble manservant.
Thanks, I appreciate
it, but I don't need a--
[CHIMP] But I insist!
From the north to the south,
your manservant is but
only a phone call away!
[AKENO] Hey...
Stop that, you scumbag!
[CHIMP] Yes! Call me scum!
I've been naughty
and need to be punished!
Alright! If this what'll
get you away from me!
[NARRATOR] As you can see,
Chimp's pride is non-existent.
[CHIMP] Thank you,
Boss of Bosses.
Can I have another?
You're really creeping
me out, Chimp.
So, you're in
charge of all the
gangs here at
school now, huh, Akeno?
I am not!
[whistle]
[SUN] Officer Mawari!
I turn my back
for a few seconds
and now there's organized
crime on campus!
[MAWARI]
As long as Mawari Zenigata--
the demonic Disciplinary
Committee member lives,
gang violence will not
be tolerated at this school!
What did you say, you runt?
Are trying to pick a fight
with our Boss of
Bosses, you runt?
Stop calling me a runt,
you big bunch of creeps!
My growth spurt is just
starting, you know!
Are you sure about that?
It doesn't
look like it to me.
Um, ya know, there are
some guys who like small girls.
[NARRATOR] As it turns out,
Maguro is one of them.
I don't have
time for nonsense.
See ya.
Hey! Wait a minute!
Come back here.
You're under arrest
for conspiracy!
[AKENO] You're just a
Disciplinary Committee Member.
[MAWARI] What did you say?
Wow, didja hear that?
Akeno's got nerves of steel!
I think she realizes
fighting's pointless.
[NARRATOR] This mature
frame of mind is
amazing in a
second-year student!
[ALL]
Wait for us, oh Boss of Bosses!
[All cry out]
Oh, Chimp? How could you?
My lord Kai!
[KAI] I picked you out
of the other riff-raff
and let you be
my right-hand man!
But now you defect
to the Shot-Caller group?
[CHIMP] Yes, my lord,
or should I say former lord.
Your reign's ended.
I only ally myself
with the most powerful.
[KAI] You ingrate!
I thought we were comrades!
Buddies! Pals! Friends!
[CHIMP] Hmph... Friends, eh?
Goodbye, my youth.
[CHIMP] Come on...
[CHIMP] Be mature
about this, would ya?
[NAGASUMI]
Kai's really upset, huh?
[NARRATOR] Kai Mikawa's
sorrow at losing a friend
is deeper than the waters
around the Ogasawara Islands.
How utterly vexing.
Hey, hold it right there! I'm
not done with you. Come back!
[beeps]
[REN] Hmm?
How'd ya get so beat
up this early in the morning?
Well, my former
superior didn't
take too kindly
to my resignation.
[REN] Huh?
[CHIMP IN A MASKED VOICE]
He was a terrible man and a
demanding boss
who only won people
over through his
money and his power.
[REN] I see.
[CHIMP] I got sick and tired of
both him and his dirty money.
So I quit following
him and joined up
with the powerful
Shot-Caller's group.
[REN] The Shot-Caller?
Who's that?
You don't know?
Who else?
The Vexingly Sexy
Akeno Shiranui.
she's the hottest thing
in school right now!
And speaking of
hot and sexy ladies,
you're looking pretty smokin'!
[REN] She's the school's
Shot-Caller, eh?
[GOZABURO THINKS]
Shot-Caller, my ass!
That Mermaid Exam's
just a crock!
You're trying to seize power!
Well, missy, I'll show
ya that the Seto's
are the strongest
things around here!
A Mermaid Exam
by sea officials, huh?
Wow, I never
imagined there was so
much red tape in
the mermaid world, Sun.
Nagasumi, ya
really shouldn't say
stuff like that out loud,
considering who
might be listening.
Oh, I'm sorry.
I'll be more careful.
That goes for you, too.
Don't spill any more
water on yourself.
Why'd ya say that?
Do ya think I'm an airhead?
[NAGASUMI] I just meant
for you to be careful!
[NARRATOR] Actually,
he said it because
Sun is indeed an airhead.
[VOICES] She is!
[MAWARI] Akeno!
You've got no
other place else to run.
So give it up.
You're quite stubborn...
Discipline Girl.
You got away last time,
but that's not gonna happen
now that I've got you cornered!
You didn't have to corner her;
she's in our class.
You...! Your luck ran
out when you got put in
the same class
as Mawari Zenigata,
daughter of the
Superintendent General,
Vexingly Sexy Shot-Caller!
[AKENO] Why?
You're just his daughter.
[GIRL A] Don't insult Mawari!
[GIRL B] Yeah, boobzilla!
[GIRL C] Stop your sexy flexing!
[AKENO] I thought
it was "Vexingly Sexy."
[NARRATOR] It is,
and Akeno's arrival has
destroyed all peace
within the school.
[MAWARI] As head of the
Disciplinary Committee
of this school,
I cannot tolerate your
criminal activities on
campus any longer, Akeno!
Cease all Vexingly
Sexy Shot-Caller
activities
immediately!
Oh wow, this thing is really
starting to get serious.
It's like gangsters
versus a crime squad,
and when things like this
happen, people go to jail!
It'll be fine, Sun,
just calm down!
This has been a
big misunderstanding.
First of all, I am not the
Vexingly Sexy Shot-Caller.
Ms. Akeno is the
Vexingly Sexy Shot-Caller,
and the Vexingly Sexy
Shot-Caller is the toughest
and hottest girl at
Isono Junior High School!
[AKENO] Shut up, you morons!
What a surprise!
The boys side with the
girl with the big boobs!
How dare they,
those dirty-minded bums!
Why do boys always have
to be such sleazebags?
[BURIO] Can it, you runts!
I told you to stop
calling me a runt!
[BURIO] But that's what you are!
Shut up! Like I said,
cease and desist at once.
But if you don't, Akeno.
Then what, Mawari?
[MAWARI] Then
in the name of this
school's Disciplinary Committee.
I'll teach you the
rules of this society!
[MAWARI] Guilty or Not Guilty?
[GIRLS] Guilty!
[chants of "Mawari"
and "Akeno."]
This is the
absolute worst.
[NARRATOR]
That's right! It is the worst!
[NAGASUMI] This
place is a powderkeg
that's about to explode!
[SUN] If we get hauled in,
they'll find out I'm a mermaid
and I'll flunk the test.
[CHIMP] Come on,
guys, step right up!
Don't be shy!
[CHIMP] You can find what you
need most in life right here!
Your one-stop shop for
all of your Akeno
Shiranui items!
New products are arriving daily
and look what we just got in!
[CHIMP] These vexingly sexy
candid pics of Akeno!
Pretty nice, huh?
[BOY A] Those are
the vexingly sexiest yet!
[BOY B] Just name your price!
I've gotta have 'em!
[BOY C] Me, too, and I'll pay
double what that guy's offering!
[CHIMP] Sold!
And speaking of which,
if you bought a raffle
ticket, it's prize time!
If your ticket has a
red circle on it,
you're the lucky winner!
[NAGASUMI] Do you
think Akeno's even
aware of what he's doing?
[SUN] Beats me...
...but I did buy this raffle
ticket with a red circle on it.
Circle? Um...
[SUN] Over here, sir!
I've got the winning ticket!
[CHIMP] Congratulations, miss!
You've just won this life-sized
Vexingly Sexy
Shot-Caller body pillow!
[SUN] Yay! I won! I won!
[NAGASUMI] Sun! Chimp
is no "Sir," and having a
body pillow of your
classmate is just...
[NARRATOR] Life-sized
body pillows are
filled with both
dreams and romance!
And they're available
for the low price of--!
Dammit, who was
it that screwed it up?
I was just about to
pull out the life size doll.
[MAWARI] We did!
Oh crap, it's you guys!
The Disciplinary Committee!
Oh no!
[MAWARI] The sale
of non-school related
merchandise is
prohibited on campus!
[CHIMP] This stuff ain't
"merchandise!" It's soul!
[MAWARI] Like that dumb
logic would work on me!
[MAWARI] Confiscate it!
[CHIMP] No, don't!
Please! I'm begging you!
I'm just a small businessman
trying to scratch out...
[GIRL A] This is so perverted!
[GIRL B] It's smut!
[CHIMP] It is not!
It's my heart, my life,
and like I said, my soul!
Please stop reaping my
soul, you grim reapers!
[GIRL D] That's all of it.
[CHIMP] I've burned up.
[NARRATOR] The "Shot-Caller
Problem Emergency
Countermeasures Meeting,"
a meeting to devise emergency
countermeasures for
the shot-caller problem
the school is currently facing.
And so, ladies...
For the sake
of school discipline,
we have to do something
about the Shot-Caller
and her gang.
I say we start at the
top and take Akeno down!
[GIRL A] We'll crush her!
[GIRL B] Let's take back
our bright, clean school!
[GIRL C] Boys suck!
[SUN] I disagree with agreement!
[MAWARI] Sun?
Sorry...
It seemed so lively.
I had to come and check it out.
[CLASS REP] "I disagree
with agreement." Interesting.
I don't get it, Sun.
Just what is that
supposed to mean?
Well... don't ya think
that maybe we're jumping
the gun a little here
by judging Akeno,
when we still don't even
know her all that well yet?
[GIRL A] Hmm...
[GIRL B] Maybe Sun's right!
[GIRL C] Yeah,
but boys still suck!
[GIRLS] Right! Boys still suck!
Well, I got no real
opinion on that, but...
Mawari?
You're right, Sun.
I did jump the gun again
for like the bazillionth time.
Then I guess...
No one has a reason
to fight now, right?
'Spose not.
[GIRLS] Of course we do!
Akeno's with the boys,
and boys suck!
[SUN] Any reason'll do, huh?
But why does everyone
still want to fight?
[NARRATOR]
Any old reason will do,
but these young ladies obviously
have something against Akeno.
[MAWARI THINKS]
I did the same thing when
Sun first transferred here.
I was suspicious of her, too,
before I ever got to know her.
That isn't right of me.
[girls continue to chant]
[GOZABURO] Well?
What's the situation?
[SHARK] She's very
popular with the boys?
And they're really buying
her merchandise?
[GOZABURO] What about the girls?
[MASA] A few words from Miss Sun
seem to have
swayed their opinion.
The situation's
in a state of flux.
[GOZABURO]
Then we gotta un-flux it!
[MASA] Huh?
[GOZABURO] That's
girl's gotta be squelched
before the day's over!
Take care of it!
She's just a kid, Boss, so I
don't feel too good about this.
[GOZABURO] I don't care
how ya feel about it Masa!
Just do your freakin'
job already, would ya?
[REN] What the hell?
What're ya up to back there?
Nothing good, I bet!
No, sweetie!
We were just back
here talkin' about, uh,
the student guidance
sessions that are comin' up!
Isn't that right?
Right!
We were discussing what
to say to the new
transfer student.
The new girl?
The one with the
bountiful cleavage?
[GOZABURO] Those things
are like missiles, aren't they?
[MASA] They've certainly
grabbed the boys' attention.
[SHARK] I'd like to
sink my teeth into her?
[GOZABURO]
So would I, but that would
earn me an express ride
to the slammer, ha ha ha!
You'll get an
express ride to
the grave if I hear
ya talk like that again!
[GOZABURO] I meant
"if I was her age and single!"
[SHARK] It didn't
sound that way to me?
[MASA] Hence Ms. Ren's response.
[MAWARI] Excuse me...
[REN] Oh, Ms. Zenigata.
[GOZABURO] Crap!
The Superintendent
General's daughter!
I'm sorry. I can come
back if this is a bad time.
[GOZABURO] No, no, not all!
Now's the perfect time
for ya talk with Ms. Ren!
Wouldn't ya say so, Masa?
[MASA] Yes!
[REN] Oh, For the love of...
[REN] So... what's wrong?
Ya worried about something?
[REN] The school's Shot-Caller?
Yes.
There's absolutely
nothing for ya to worry about.
Me and some of
the other teachers here
have dealt with gangs before,
so we know how
to put the screws to--
Um, I mean, we know
how to handle them!
[MAWARI]
No, that's not it.
I'm a member of the
Disciplinary Committee,
and should know
better, but I almost
instigated half the
school to attack Akeno.
[REN] Even so,
being a sea official,
Akeno could have
taken them all on and won.
The thing is...
I never gave Akeno
the benefit of the doubt.
I don't know her but
I assumed the worst because
there was something about
her that made me suspicious.
[REN THINKS] I wonder if
it's the police blood
in her that makes
her suspicious.
[MAWARI]
And for that...
I hate myself. And I'm
sure she hates me, too!
[REN] It's okay...
If ya ask me,
you're being way too
hard on yourself, sweetie.
You weren't really
being suspicious.
You were just being cautious.
But still...
[REN] Considering your family's
line of work,
I can't say I blame ya.
But you're a good kid.
Gee, thanks, Ms. Ren,
but what makes you say that?
[REN] Well, for one,
the fact that you're
in here telling me about this.
It means ya have a conscience,
and it made ya do
some soul-searching.
Ya realized ya
made a mistake today,
and ya owned up to it, too.
That's why you're good.
You think so?
Hey, let me see a smile!
Ya don't always
have to be so serious!
[REN THINKS] On the other hand,
there are certain people
around here who
aren't serious enough!
They don't do a
lick of soul-searching,
and unlike her,
they're no good at all!
[group laughing]
[NARRATOR] Children,
don't grow up to be like this.
Like I was saying,
we'll put the screws
to this Shot-Caller
gang, um, I mean,
we'll give them the
guidance they need,
so don't worry about it, okay?
[MAWARI]
'Kay...!
Thanks for everything, ma'am!
You're welcome, and ya
don't have to be so formal.
[CLASS REP] Mawari!
What is it?
Um, all the girls
are about to fight!
I've got quite a bit
to do this afternoon.
So if you insist on this,
you're gonna have
to make it quick.
Yeah! The Shot-Caller's
a busy woman,
so you ladies better
make it snappy!
[GIRL A] Why, is she too
busy with her boobs?
[GIRL B] She looks
down on us 'cause
she's got a better body!
[GIRL C] Let's teach
Boobzilla a lesson!
[AKENO] It seems
like their reason
for disliking me has changed.
[CHIMP] It looks like any
old reason'll do at this point.
[NARRATOR]
In this case, it's because the
girls are jealous
of Akeno's assets!
This is ridiculous.
I don't have time
for any more of this
nonsense today,
so I'm going home now.
[BURIO] Hold it,
Vexingly Sexy Shot-Caller!
[CHIMP] What are
you guys doing over there?
The Shot-Caller's over here!
The three of us
have decided that the
whole "Shot-Caller"
thing was a little passé, gyo.
[AKENO]
Your outfits say otherwise.
Someone has
to protect the girls
and carry out
discipline in this school,
and who better than us, gyo?
\We'll bring order
to the chaos
and the girls
will all admire us!
[NARRATOR] Yes, that's
their true motivation,
the cry of their souls.
You backstabbing traitors
are just trying
to start a harem!
Look, I don't care
who you hook up with.
And if you want to carry
out discipline, then fine.
But it's got nothing
to do with me!
So stop following me around!
You heard the lady,--
You, too, you
pervy Chimp!
Time to settle this,
Vexingly Sexy Shot-Caller!
Once we defeat you,
we'll be the toughest
in this school!
And after I spared
your miserable lives!
Ingrates!
No mercy this time!
[GIRLS] Mawari?
I, Mawari Zenigata,
the Demonic Disciplinary
Committee member
of Isono Eighth,
hereby order you to
cease this pointless fight!
I will not tolerate it!
[crazy cat mewing]
[Burio screams]
[BURIO] There's so many of them!
And they're hungry, too!
[GIRLS] Oh, no, it's too much!
Wow, I'm actually impressed!
I didn't realize
Mawari had gotten
so good at controlling cats!
[MAWARI] No! Stop!
[MAWARI] Hey, you kittens aren't
supposed to be attacking me!
[CHIMP] I guess she's
not controlling them.
[MAWARI] Come on,
you guys, knock it off!
You know you
shouldn't be doing this!
Leave me alone!
What's the deal
with all these cats?
They're clingier
than that pervy Chimp!
[AKENO] Stop it! Scat! No!
Why are you trying
to go in there?
[NARRATOR] Because
even cats, it seems,
can't resist the bountiful
cleavage of Akeno Shiranui!
Things were going
smoothly until
the Superintendent General's
daughter showed up!
It seems like our
plan to take care
of Akeno by turning the girls
against her failed, Boss.
Then it's hopeless
now, I guess?
Hey, don't interrupt
me, I'm tryin' to think!
I mean it, Masa, or I'm
gonna take that frizzy,
crispy noodle head
of yours and--
I knew the three
of ya were up to no good!
No, honey, wait!
This is all a big
misunderstanding!
I can explain!
[NARRATOR] Children,
don't grow up to be like this.
[GIRLS] Please, no!
Stop it! We can't
take any more of this!
Oh, well,
I guess I should
look on the bright side.
At least I managed
to stop the other girls
from having a pointless
fight with Akeno!
[HAWKISH GIRLS] These cats can't
keep us from the real enemy!
[HAWKISH GIRL A]
Did you really think a few,
mangy cats would stop us,
the extremist faction of the
Disciplinary Committee?
[HAWKISH GIRL B]
Don't try to interfere with us,
Mawari, or we'll
convict you as well!
[HAWKISH GIRLS] That's right!
Stay out of our way!
No, guys wait.
[HAWKISH GIRL B]
Guilty, or not guilty, girls?
[HAWKISH GIRLS] Guilty!
You can't...
Don't waste your breath;
they're determined to fight.
[AKENO] I was hoping
to avoid this. Oh, well...
[MAWARI THINKS] Oh, no!
This is really gonna happen!
What am I supposed to do?
I can't stop everyone!
[REN] Thirty against one?
How 'bout I even
the odds a little?
[FISH BROTHERS]
Ms. Ren!
Ya know, girls...
This is very disappointing.
All of you are members
of the Disciplinary Committee.
You're supposed
to be good examples
fer the other students.
[REN] But here
you are ganging up
on one person just like a bunch
of no-good scumbags would!
[girls exclaim surprise]
Here I was thinking
the Disciplinary Committee
was supposed
to be better than this.
But you're acting like
thugs lookin' to fight!
[REN] Well, if it's
a fight ya want,
then it's a fight
you're gonna get.
[REN] But with me!
I'll take ya all on!
She's so amazing!
Oh what were
we thinking?
There's only one woman we
should be following... Ms. Ren!
However...
Ya see, ya can just
walk away from this.
[REN] Instead of fighting,
ya could try to
get to know your
new classmate better.
That's good advice.
There's only
one gang for us,
and that's the Seto gang!
[MAGURO] We were wrong to try
and start our own gang, Ms. Ren!
Please forgive us!
[HAWKISH GIRL B] We owe
you an apology, Akeno!
[HAWKISH GIRL C] We were mean
to you for the dumbest reason!
[HAWKISH GIRL A]
We were just so jealous
of your bountiful cleavage!
[NARRATOR] Yes,
that's their true motivation,
the cry of their souls.
My, what a
fuss over nothing.
[AKENO] Thanks,
but try not to stand out.
I appreciate the help,
but that doesn't
excuse you from my Mermaid Exam.
Don't worry...
I won't screw up,
and all I did back there
was what any teacher would have
done in the same situation.
[MAWARI] Akeno...
[MAWARI] I'm so sorry!
This all happened because
I made a rash decision!
Don't worry about it.
It's over now.
You'll make a fine
Superintendent General one day.
Thank you, Akeno.
And with that,
she walked off into the sunset.
[NARRATOR]
The Shot-Caller's crisis at
Isono Eighth Junior High
has finally passed.
[NARRATOR] But it's not
an easy road she walks,
and surely more challengers
will impede her path.
[NARRATOR]
Yippee-Ki-Yay, Akeno Shiranui,
the Vexingly Sexy Shot-Caller!
[SUN] Huh? So this
was that kind of story?
I guess so, but we hardly
had any lines in it, huh?
[MASA] Boss...
Maybe we should
learn from this, ya know?
Not try to pull
anything like this again?
Boss?
Boss!
♪
[KAI] This is the end.
Nothing can save me.
[CHIMP] My lord! My lord!
Your humble servant
has returned!
I beg your forgiveness, my lord!
Please allow me take my rightful
place by your side again!
[KAI] Chimp!
[NAGASUMI]
A surprise field trip?
Mr. Seto, be more careful!
Akeno's Mermaid Exam
is still going on,
and so is psychological
warfare between men and
women set against
the backdrop of Kyoto!
I can't let tasty food and
hot baths distract me!
This is a war zone!
What?
Sun's practicing in the bathtub?