[LUNAR'S PAPA] Affirmative.
Buy all of those.
[LUNAR'S PAPA] Correct.
Sell all of those.
I'll be back in
forty-eight hours.
I need a vacation.
Don't interrupt me.
Hasta la vista.
[beeps]
A gift from a rival?
[LUNAR'S PAPA] Hmph! Nice try,
but that little obstacle
can't terminate
my vacation plans.
Wait for me, Lunar.
[NARRATOR]
Several dozen leagues from
the Inland Sea's foam.
Lies the land of Saitama,
birthplace and home.
But where'er you go,
the demons still roam.
A violent mob's on the scene.
Watching the
schoolboy's routine.
And poor Nagasumi
is only fourteen.
Like a stormy sea, the course of
this love is
anything but smooth.
♪
[MAWARI] Alright,
stay in line, people!
No cutting!
Proceed in an
orderly fashion!
[NAGASUMI THINKS]
Wow! That's Sun for you!
She looks beautiful
in every picture!
You're gonna
request extras prints
of those pictures, aren't you?
You're such a cliché.
What's the problem
with that?
[CHIMP] My lord!
My lord, I found one!
A photo of me? Really?
Yes, I did, my lord,
and one in--
Yeah, but you can't
even tell it's him.
With that stupid helmet on,
he just looks like an astronaut.
[CHIMP] Yes, my lord!
[KAI] I'll even get ya a
hundred for yourself, Chimp!
Check it out, gyo!
We look so cool, gyo!
That field trip was
awesome, wasn't it, gyo?
The handsome samurai
are up in the house, gyo!
[NAGASUMI] Well at
least somebody had
some fun on that crazy trip.
[SUN] Nagasumi.
Oh, hi Sun.
Are ya sayin' ya didn't
have any fun at all on the trip?
Um, well...
[NAGASUMI] I had fun,
but the main thing
I remember about the trip,
was all the scary and dangerous
things that happened on it.
[SUN] Lunar...
Oh wow, you really
look exhausted.
[LUNAR] We are...
We wrapped our
movie this morning
and then came straight here.
It's tough being
a big movie star, huh?
All work and no play and
you even missed the field trip.
Yeah, It's too
bad that we only got
to see ya when we
stopped at Movieland.
We had loads of fun;
it was the best field trip ever!
[NAGASUMI] Huh?
[LUNAR] We're a
world-famous pop star!
We don't have time
to take field trips,
so stop telling us about
how great it was!
Sorry, we thought
maybe you wanted
to hear about some
of the stuff you missed.
[LUNAR] No, we don't!
[LUNAR] No, we don't,
because we really wish
we could have been there.
[NAGASUMI]
What do we do with her?
Lunar...
Would some yummy yatsuhashi
from Kyoto cheer ya up?
[LUNAR] No, it wouldn't!
Crackers, then?
Wow, Lunar, I guess your
sorrow's deeper
than the sea, huh?
[LUNAR] I hate 'em!
Stupid field trips!
[NAGASUMI]
You've made that clear.
I coulda sworn
I saw something.
What the heck
are you doing
here at school, Lunar's Papa?
Well...
I needed a vacation,
so I thought I'd come
here to check on my little girl.
You do that by peeking
at her through the window?
Yes, your point
being, human?
[NAGASUMI] Well,
what you're doing
is actually more like stalking.
[LUNAR'S PAPA] Negative.
It is parent-child bonding.
[NAGASUMI] Oh yeah, sure,
whatever you say!
[LUNAR'S PAPA] I pity her.
She's not able to enjoy
her youth like the rest of you.
The field trip to Kyoto,
for example.
[NAGASUMI THINKS] Wow...
He does seem really
concerned about her.
[NAGASUMI] I felt really bad
about her and
the field trip, too...
Lunar's Papa.
I have a question I
want you to answer.
[NAGASUMI] Yes?
You, human... What
is it that I should do?
[NAGASUMI] Huh?
[LUNAR'S PAPA] I failed
in my mission to make
my wife happy, and she was a
woman I thought I loved.
[LUNAR'S PAPA]
In order to atone for
not achieving that objective,
I swore to make Lunar happy,
so I've given her the world.
She's never wanted for anything.
[LUNAR'S PAPA]
But even so, my Lunar...
She's still not satisfied,
right? That's it, isn't it?
[LUNAR'S PAPA] Why does she cry?
What else should I give her?
She doesn't need more
money or material things.
[LUNAR'S PAPA] Hm?
[NAGASUMI] She's pretty
happy at my place,
and it's definitely not
a five-star hotel.
The only weird
thing is she doesn't
seem to be able to
stand up to my mom.
[MOM] Lunar, dear, you have
some rice on your face.
[NAGASUMI] Lunar's Papa?
I see...
So it is not she who
is truly pitiful, but me.
What are you talking about?
Hey, look...
There's no
reason to mope.
Why don't you go
in there and comfort
her about missing
the field trip?
Go do some
parent-child bonding, 'kay?
Will it work?
Sure it will!
You're her father.
Now get in there
and cheer her up.
But, what should
I say to her, human?
Maybe "Hey, let's
go on a trip together,"
or something like that.
Lunar.
[LUNAR] Papa?
[SUN] Does he ever enter
a room through the door?
[NAGASUMI] Nope.
Well, what is it that
you want, Papa?
[NAGASUMI THINKS] Say
something that'll cheer her up!
Lunar...
You are pitiful.
Let us got to Dubai.
[LUNAR] Who are
you calling pitiful?
[LUNAR] And explain
why going to Dubai
is the solution
if we're so pitiful?
[NAGASUMI THINKS] Oh, man, maybe
I gave him the wrong advice!
What did I do wrong?
I still don't understand
my daughter's heart.
[sirens]
[VOICES] Papa's place!
[LUNAR'S PAPA]
"Girls' hearts." Negative.
"Modern young girls' hearts." In
other words, "modern gals."
[LUNAR'S PAPA] So the
keyword to search for is...
"Gal Games?" It brings
up a number of hits.
This has to be my target.
[LUNAR'S PAPA] It's me.
I need all the following
products immediately.
The titles are--
[CHIMP] Hey, Sun, come on!
Time for school!
What the--
[CHIMP] Lunar,
you're off work today?
Wow, that's rare!
We're off work for the
next few weeks, actually.
Hey, Chimp.
Oh... good mornin', Chimp.
Ah, looking at Sun
really wakes me up!
Yeah, whatever...
Let's get moving.
[SUN] Ya sure are in a bad mood
this mornin', huh, Lunar?
[LUNAR] You would be too,
if you finally got a break from
work and it was
after the field trip!
[NAGASUMI] So that's why, huh?
I'll be happy to help
ya with the research
paper assignment ya
missed while ya were gone.
You should just let
us put our name on yours.
No, that would
be cheating!
Whatever!
Some friend you are,
Miss Goody Two-Shoes!
Hey, watch where
you're going, you stupid--
[LUNAR] Pa--
[LUNAR'S PAPA] Negative.
This set of choices
is for Akiharu,
the main character of the game.
Today I have
to play the heroine,
and as a result,
react to Lunar's choices.
(high pitched voice)
Akiharu, uh, I mean, Lunar!
You slept in, too? Not again!
Look what happens
when I don't wake you up!
You're so bad!
[LUNAR'S PAPA] Lunar, hold up!
Wait for me, please!
What the--
Was that who
I thought it was?
Uh huh, and if
my dad did something
like that in front
of me, I'd just die.
[alarm bell ringing]
[baby crying]
[SUN] He's still wearing
that school uniform.
But why? Why?
Oh make him stop, please!
M-M-Maybe
I sh-should teach
you the r-r-rules
of this s-society.
Hey, why's the
alarm goin' off?
So you're the reason someone
set off the alarm! Huh?
(high-pitched voice] Oh, dear!
I'm so sorry, Mr. Seto!
Not as sorry as
you're gonna be
when I'm done kickin' your butt!
[LUNAR'S PAPA] Oh, dear!
[GOZABURO]
Let's take this outside!
[LUNAR'S PAPA] Yessir!
[GOZABURO] So you're
Cross-dressin' now, huh?
I never figured ya
for the type Edomae.
[LUNAR'S PAPA]
{normal voice] Negative.
I'm only doing this
for my daughter's sake.
What?
Can you say you
understand your daughter?
Do you know why she cries?
Wait, don't tell me
your cross-dressin'
has somethin' to do with this!
Yes...
The father-daughter bond
between me and Lunar
is in danger of
being terminated,
like yours and Sun's.
It's in danger?
[GOZABURO] Well,
now that ya mention it,
ya might have a
point there, Edomae.
When Sun said she was gonna
marry that maggot,
I had no clue what
my little girl was thinkin'.
Gozaburo Seto...
We are both trying to make up
for failing to understand
our daughters.
I have involved
myself personally in the
life of mine while
you watch yours afar.
Hey...!
Are ya sayin' I haven't
been tryin' as hard to
understand my daughter
as ya have with yours?
Yes.
So do ya have
any advice on what
else I can do
for her at this point,
aside from watchin' over her?
Use this and you
will have no problemo.
[GOZABURO] Huh?
"After School Love Hearts?"
[school bells chime]
Fujishiro...
Do you not have
a class to teach?
Oh, yeah, I guess
I do? So what?
You got a problem
with that or something?
Not really?
If that's so, then how come
you're not doing your job?
I didn't swear an oath to
the Seto outfit to play teacher?
In this place, all I am
is a glorified babysitter?
So yeah...
I guess I do
have a problem?
[MASA] I see...
Then you've also got a problem
with the Boss's orders!
[MASA] In our world,
if the Boss calls
something a spade, it's a spade.
Period. Got it?
[MASA] What the
Boss says is absolute!
[MASA] Are you going back
on the oath you swore to him?
Let me remind
you that an oath
isn't something
to be taken lightly.
Hey there guys!
We gotta beat this game
so I can solve my problem!
[MASA] Huh?
[GOZABURO] Now accordin'
to what I've heard,
there's lots of
girls in this game.
It's all about how they think
and feel and act and stuff.
We're each gonna
play as one of
these characters here
and then we're gonna
memorize all the
things they do and say!
So take your pick!
Hold on what? Boss.
And why would we do that?
Well isn't it obvious?
By playin' as these girls,
we're gonna learn
how they think and act,
and experience what
they're feelin' in their hearts!
This game is gonna help me
understand what's
goin' on in Sun's heart!
[MASA] What... no Boss.
I don't--
I thought what the Boss
said was absolute?
[dog howls]
[FISH BROTHERS]
Gyo, gyo, gyo, gyo...
[GIRL NEXT DOOR]
Akiharu, you slept in, too?
Look what happens
when I don't wake you up!
You're going to have a tough
future if you don't shape up!
Bad boy!
[TSUNDERE] Forget him.
You need to leave
Akiharu alone sometimes.
It'll do him good
to get in trouble.
[GOZABURO]
"Boo hoo."
[LITTLE SISTER] Big brother,
you forgot something!
Here, take your lunch box.
[GOZABURO]
"Oh, sorry, sorry."
[BARBARELLA] Oh, look meow-t!
[BARBARELLA] Meow.
If I didn't have a cushion,
that would've been dangerous!
[GOZABURO] "Who're
you calling a 'cushion?'"
[BARBARELLA] My cushion
is grumbling, meow!
[GOZABURO] "Anyway,
you do realize I can
see your underwear, right?"
[GOZABURO]
"Ugh?"
[BARBARELLA] Pervy humans
get the death penalty, meow!
[GOZABURO]
"Boo hoo?"
[GOZABURO] Huh?
What the hell's goin' on?
When do I get to start
playin' this damn game?
[MASA] Actually, I think you've
already started
playing it, Boss.
[SHARK] Which one's the enemy?
None of them.
It says here that the
goal of the game
is to set off
something called "flags."
[GOZABURO] "Flags?" What, like
Capture the Flag or somethin'?
A buncha grown
men sittin' around
playin' gal games is just gross!
Oh, come, on,
give 'em a break!
It's just harmless fun, gyo!
Yeah, and I remember
we used
to play a few
of them ourselves, gyo!
Not a few,
but a lot, gyo!
Gyo, gyo, gyo, gyo!
Disgustin'!
[BURIO] Gyo!
Let's see... One,
two, three, four, fix, six:
Hey, that makes Haneman!
[MAKI] Zugan!
What the hell?
Hey, why can't I flirt
with the school nurse!
[MASA] It says here she's
just a side character.
Crap!
Well, if I can't flirt with her,
I might as well drown her!
[SHARK] It won't let
you do that, either?
[MASA] All due respect,
I don't know if you
can really understand
a girl's heart this way.
[GOZABURO] Don't give
me that crap, ya moron!
I'm gonna become totally
moe, no matter what!
Ya hear me?
[NAGASUMI] Oh, Sun.
[MASA] Big brother.
Big brother.
[NAGASUMI] Huh?
What big brother? Is that me?
[LITTLE SISTER] Big brother!
[MASA] Hey, there.
Big brother, oh please wake up.
[NAGASUMI] M-M-M-M-M-Masa?
No, I'm not Masa.
I'm your little sister.
I'm Masako.
[NAGASUMI] What the
heck are you talking about?
[MASA] Big brother,
please answer me honestly.
--Please tell us, Big brother.
--[MASA] Do you think I'm moe?
[NAGASUMI] What? M-Moe?
What I'm asking
is if I have
little sister moe going on.
[NAGASUMI] I don't
understand what you mean.
[MASA] I see.
For that matter,
what is moe, anyway?
Masa?
You okay?
Are you having a mid-life
crisis or something?
[MAKI] Look closer, sea louse!
[NAGASUMI] Maki!
What you're seein'
now is a real man!
[MASA] Maki?
A man so committed
to helping the
Boss better understand
Sun that he'll do anything,
including dressing
up like a girl!
Oh, by the way...
that ribbon looks cute on ya!
It does? I look good?
[MAKI] Ya look moe to me!
Real moe!
Oh, so that's why.
It's all because of something
Sun's Dad is up to.
[LUNAR'S PAPA]
{high-pitched voice) Oh, no!
Don't look at me, you jerk!
Him, too, huh.
I've been told
that Mr. Edomae
is doing "the girl
who lives next door" moe.
That's what the
anguish of a man with
a teenage daughter
looks like, sea louse!
No! I don't want
to go to school today!
Miss Sun, why not?
What on earth's the matter?
If you don't hurry,
you'll be late for class, Sun!
[MAKI] Please, Miss Sun,
you've gotta go!
The Boss is waitin' for
ya there in full moe mode!
[SUN] No, I said
I don't wanna go!
[LUNAR] Come on, Sun!
You have to
suffer the same agony
that we did yesterday,
so move it!
[SUN] No!
[GOZABURO]
(high-pitched voice) Meow-llo!
[VOICES] Class 2-1's
Cosplaying Teacher! Yay!
[GOZABURO] Hi, there, Sun!
Nice to meet you!
My name is Gozakko!
Pretty strong wind
today, huh, Lunar?
Yeah. We'll say.
It's dried all
of our tears away.
Maybe I should just
run away and disappear.
We'll go with you.
[GOZABURO] Sun! Meow!
[LUNAR'S PAPA] Lunar!
Why did you run
away all of a sudden?
If there's something
troubling you,
tell us all ab-meow-t it!
We're here to listen!
Uguu!
You're the ones
who are troublin' us!
[GOZABURO] They must
be having a rebellious phase!
[LUNAR'S PAPA] Oh, dear!
No, they're
upset about those
crazy getups
their fathers are in!
[NAGASUMI]
You're also weirding out the
students and no one's learning!
You're supposed to
be fathers and teachers,
so do something to fix this!
[GOZABURO] Uguu!
[MASA] Could we have a
minute of your time, please?
[GOZABURO] Masa! Fujishiro!
Things have taken an unexpected
turn and I'm in trouble!
Give meow some advice, you two!
Boss, look.
The two of us
have talked things over.
[MASA] This isn't easy
to say, but we've decided to
take back our oaths to the Seto
outfit and stop working for you.
[SHARK] We're sorry, Boss?
[LUNAR'S PAPA] Oh!
[GOZABURO] What?
I can't believe
you two have made
things even meow-ore
complicated!
[NAGASUMI THINKS] Oh, yeah?
Well, I can't believe
these guys have endured
working for you
as long as they did!
[GOZABURO]
What'll I do without you? Meow!
[LUNAR'S PAPA]
This is a real problemo!
[SUN] Don't ya see
now how much trouble
you're causin' for all
the people around ya?
It's time ya
knocked this stuff off!
Hurry and get out
of those stupid outfits!
Oh, dear!
This is an even bigger
problemo than I thought!
But all we're
trying to do is
understand our
daughters better--
No, you're
embarrassin' us!
(regular voice) Open your mind.
Quoting a movie
won't cut it!
[GOZABURO] Please don't
be angry with me-ow!
It'll hurt me-ow if you are!
[LUNAR PAPA] (high-pitched
voice) Oh dear!
[SUN AND LUNAR]
No, stay away from us!
Stop it! Perverts!
[GOZABURO] (regular voice)
R-Ren!
What are ya doin' walkin' around
with Maki in broad daylight?
What's she doin' here anyway?
Maki couldn't bear
to watch this anymore,
so she came to get me.
[REN] We made sure
to keep people away.
[MAWARI] The roof
is currently closed
due to Seto family issues!
Nothing to see up there, folks!
[CLASS REP] That's right!
So please stop trying to
push your way through! 'Kay?
If any of you
attempt to get by,
you'll have to
go through me first.
[STUDENTS] It's the shot-caller!
How vexing.
Um, hey, Akeno...
Do have any clue what's
going on upstairs?
Exactly what
you said, Mawari.
Seto family issues.
(high-pitched voice)
I stayed up all night
researching by
playing games, meow!
What'd I do wrong, meow!
Are the cat ears a
little too much, meow?
You still don't
get it, do you?
Did I dress up as the
wrong character, meow?
(regular voice)
Perhaps. Maybe you should
have dressed as a "Tsundere"
classmate instead.
(regular voice)
You're right!
Wrong, ya morons!
[GOZABURO AND LUNAR'S PAPA]
Oh, dear!
[SUN] Let's go, Lunar.
We'll go live a
quiet life someplace
far away where nobody knows us.
[LUNAR] Right...
Our lives here are over now.
This isn't good!
(high-pitched voice) Maki,
you understand, right, meow?
Tell 'em, meow!
Look boss!
By dressin' up like that,
it's painfully obvious
how much ya love your daughter!
[MAKI] But... But...!
[MAKI] But I think ya might've
gone a little too far this time.
Both of you listen here...
Ya meant well, but fathers
tryin' to understand
their daughters is a
mistake to begin with.
[REN] A big one!
[LUNAR'S PAPA] Oh, dear.
If ya wanna
understand your little
girls' hearts better,
here's some advice.
Set a good example
for your daughters!
That's the opposite
of what ya just did!
[REN] Those two
grew up watchin' you.
Now look 'em square in the face!
[REN] If ya look at
'em full on like this,
you'll see yourselves
in 'em, am I right?
[REN] Those eyes have always
been reflections of you.
[REN] It doesn't matter what
high hopes ya set or don't set.
[REN] Those girls,
just as they are, are the
measure of you,
so take a good, long look.
Go on...
I'll think you'll see
two girls who need
their dads to be
good and nothin' else.
You're amazing, Miss Ren.
(regular voice)
Mothers are so wise. Lunar...
Sorry I upset you.
Yeah, you should be.
Thanks a lot, steel-for-brains.
(regular voice) Well...
I guess I lost my grip there.
Good thing that doesn't
happen too often.
Actually, it does,
and several times a day.
[GOZABURO] I don't
need these anymore.
[MASA] Oh good.
Hey that's great!
Sun...
I'm sorry, sweetie.
It's all right now
that ya stopped, Dad!
Now I'm gonna
do my best to forget
this crazy moe
thing ever happened.
Consider that a present
from dear, old dad, ya see.
Th-Th-Th-Th-That looks...!
Miss Sun, you're m-m-m-m--!
[GOZABURO] You're moe!
[LUNAR'S PAPA] That's it!
[SUN] What'd ya say?
I'll show ya moe,
ya stupid jerks!
[CLASS REP] Oh, hey, did you
guys hear what happened?
Mr. Seto's in the hospital
with full-body injuries.
Yeah... I heard that
if Nurse Ren hadn't been
there when he got hurt,
he might've died.
The Seto's must have
some really serious issues!
[LUNAR] Man, today sucked!
Nothing good happened.
I think I actually
miss working. Huh.
Um, Sun...
I heard your dad was
hospitalized for
full-body bruising, complex
fractures, blood loss,
and even emotional instability.
Oh, that happens
to him all the time.
Always has, ya see.
[NAGASUMI THINKS]
Yeah, I'll bet!
I think he was
just trying to get
closer to you, but
in his own, weird way.
It'll do him some
good to sit in the
hospital and think about
how he embarrassed me.
Come on,
it wasn't that bad.
Actually, those cat ears were
pretty cute on you, Su--!
[SUN] Now you're
acting like Dad, too?
Ew, gross!
What is it with everyone today?
Sun acts all
embarrassed and
uncomfortable
about stuff like that.
But you know,
I bet she secretly likes it.
Yeah?
Ears? Gross!
[SUN] Am I nuts?
What the heck am I doin'?
No, please don't stop!
[GOZABURO]
Havin' a teenage daughter's
really tough, ain't it, Edomae?
[LUNAR'S PAPA] Yes...
♪
[SEXY VOICE]
"The Girl and the Kitten."
[LUNAR'S PAPA]
An abandoned kitty cat?
Aw, you poor little thing.
It's okay. Come with me.
[LUNAR'S PAPA] Ow...
You've got some
claws there, kitty.
Come with me.
[MASA] Big sis.
[LUNAR'S PAPA] Masako.
Big sis...
If you take another
stray cat home,
father won't allow
you to keep it.
I guess there's
no persuading you.
In that case, it looks like
I'll just have to beg
Father with you.
[LUNAR'S PAPA]
Sorry for the trouble.
Oh big sis.
[NAGASUMI] What?
Another cat? No way!
[MASA AND LUNAR'S PAPA]
Nyighty-nyight!
[NAGASUMI] Oh, man,
I want to be so popular
with chicks,
it's driving me crazy!
Isn't that every guy's dream?
Well thanks to a mermaid potion,
my dream's becoming a reality!
Alright!
Oh, now I'm too popular!
I don't know if I want
this dream anymore!
Hey, wait, aren't you the
girl from that day in the--?