[CAPTAIN SWORDSMAN] And so with
that last subject evaluated,
the Mermaid Exams for the
Kansai region are now complete.
[YOSHIUO] Dude, that is
such a drag! I don't wanna
hear about boring stuff like
that, so pipe down, would ya?
Yes.
[YOSHIUO] Yo, Akeno, baby.
Yes. Lord?
[YOSHIUO] I've been
telling you like, forever,
that I think Sun from
the Seto outfit is a
major hottie who
I wanna hook up with.
Your mission was
to break her and
that lame-o human up, but you,
like, totally dropped the ball!
What the hell?
My apologies, my lord.
Apologies don't mean crap!
Well I guess if you, like,
want something done,
do it yourself!
[YOSHIUO] Make yourself useful
and like, deliver that for me.
[AKENO] That?
[YOSHIUO]
It's an invitation to a
killer party I'm gonna throw.
It's for the Seto's,
they'll, like, have to come!
[AKENO] But Lord Yoshiuo...
[YOSHIUO] Akeno, baby!
Do your job,
'cause if you don't,
I'm gonna lose my cool,
and you're not gonna like that!
[YOSHIUO]
This party's gonna rock.
It'll be one that
no one'll ever forget!
[Yoshiuo laughs]
[NARRATOR] Several dozen leagues
from the Inland Sea's foam,
Lies the land of Saitama,
birthplace and home,
But where'er you go,
the demons still roam.
A violent mob's on the scene.
Watching the
schoolboy's routine.
And poor Nagasumi
is only fourteen.
Like a stormy sea,
the course of this love
is anything but smooth.
♪
[birds chirping]
[voices on television]
[MAIN CHARACTER]
So they're coming after us?
Fine! Bring 'em on!
I'm ready!
Enemy at four o'clock, sir!
[NAGASUMI] Man!
"I-dam" reruns are the best way
to spend Sunday mornings!
[SUN] Nagasumi?
Hey there Sun...
What is it?
I've asked ya
to turn your socks
inside out before I wash 'em,
but ya didn't do it again.
How many times
to I have to tell ya?
Sorry, I guess I just forgot.
That's not the
only thing ya forgot.
Ya left tissues in
your jeans again, too.
Oh... I did, huh?
Good thing I noticed
before I put 'em into
the washin' machine,
because if they'd gotten
washed like this, there'd be
tissue flecks everywhere!
Right. I'm sorry.
I'll be more careful next time.
But that's what
ya always say, Nagasumi!
Ya never listen to me anymore
and tune out
whatever I'm sayin'.
Sorry, what was that?
[NAGASUMI] Man...
This show's the greatest.
I could watch it all day.
Hey, what'd you do that for?
'Cause...
...you're just watchin'
TV and not listenin'
to a single thing I've said to
ya for the umpteenth time!
Yeah, well, you still
didn't have to turn it off!
[NAGASUMI] Hey! Lunar's
being interviewed on TV!
[MOM] Oh, how exciting!
[DAD] Let's see!
Well... My debut album
was released when I was
twelve and I'm now in my
second year of junior high!
But I'm just
an ordinary girl!
[MOM] My goodness!
Well, this must be why
she left so early this morning.
[NAGASUMI] Isn't she amazing?
[SUN] Nagasumi,
listen to me!
[NAGASUMI] Can't it
wait a second, Sun?
Lunar's on TV.
[DAD] Oh, man,
I still can't believe we
have a pop star
living in our house!
This is so incredible!
No, to be honest,
I'm actually
staying at a friend's
house right now.
It's nice,
even if it is a little dinky!
[DAD] Dinky?
Wow! Only the most
famous celebrities get
interviewed on this show;
Lunar's movin' up!
I can remember when
you first told me about her.
You've been a big fan
of hers from the start.
I liked her the first
moment I saw her.
I guess you could say.
it was love at first sight.
[SUN] Oh, yeah?
Well, if ya love
Lunar that much,
ya should've gotten
engaged to her!
She's "love at first sight"
but I wasn't, huh?
[NAGASUMI]
But, when we first met,
I wasn't thinking of love.
I was kinda drowning, remember?
Miss Sun, I'm sure
the sea louse here
only said he'd marry ya
so he could stay alive.
I hate to break it
to ya like this, but...
...he isn't really
in love with ya!
Well, is that true?
Is that why ya haven't been
payin' any attention to me?
How could you say that?
Of course not.
I mean, sure, in the beginning,
I did agree to marry you because
the situation
called for it, but...
[Sun gasps]
[SUN] Okay, Nagasumi.
I understand how ya feel now.
Sun, wait...
I guess...
I guess in the end,
the two of us are just
a couple for show
and nothin' else, huh?
Well what's that
supposed to mean?
[MOM] You two are
having a lover's spat?
That's unusual.
[DAD] I'd apologize
if I were you.
Trust me: women
can hold a grudge.
That's right...
If only your father
knew of some of the
things I've done to
him when I was angry.
What are you
talking about, honey?
[MOM] She could put
something in your food,
or up the amount of
your life insurance policy.
Who knows; she might even
do something really scary!
Maybe we
should talk later.
Uh-uh! No way!
I didn't do anything wrong!
There's no way
I'm apologizing to Sun!
[CHIMP] From what I hear,
Nagasumi and Sun
had a fight yesterday!
They do seem to be ignoring
each other right now.
A fight?
[CLASS REP THINKS] I'm so sorry
to hear that, Nagasumi.
I'd love to comfort you,
if only I could.
Nagasumi...
You were fighting?
That's not like you.
Why don't you tell
me what happened?
You?
But you're just a
mousy glasses girl.
[CLASS REP] Look at the real me.
Hold on, you're that girl!
[NAGASUMI] The Last Amazoness!
[CLASS REP] Ha hah ha!
That's right, it is I,
the Last Amazoness,
the woman-loving
descendent of her
warrior tribe who's
on the hunt for Sun!
And I will make her mine!
[CLASS REP] I forgot!
When I take my glasses off,
I'm an Amazoness!
[CLASS REP]
Guess I'll have to live my
whole life as a glasses girl!
[VOICES] You know you'll
be in glasses for life!
[MAWARI] I don't get it.
Why are you depressed
about them fighting?
[MAWARI] Hey, Sun...?
Is it true that you had
a big fight with Nagasumi?
That's Officer Mawari for ya!
All knowing and all seeing?
It's just "Mawari."
So anyway,
what started the fight?
His dirty socks!
Dirty socks?
[MAWARI THINKS] I've got ten
thousand misdemeanor files
inputted into my brain,
but I'm not finding
any matches for any
dirty sock-related crimes!
[SUN] I know
it must sound silly,
but it's a big issue to me!
Maybe Nagasumi'll
realize he's upset
you and apologize soon.
Ya really think so?
I'm sure he will, so
come on, Sun, cheer up.
Okay! Thanks, Mawari.
There's no need
to thank me, Sun!
Feel free to come to
me for help anytime!
[door opens and closes]
How vexing.
What?
Sun and Nagasumi had
a fight and aren't talkin'?
Is that true?
Yes, my lord.
[KAI] I heard about the fight.
Hey, Kai...
Thanks, but I don't need any--
And I couldn't be happier!
I'll bet anythin'
that Sun hates ya with
all her heart now,
ya dumb bastard!
That's it, my lord!
Finish him off!
[NAGASUMI]
Knock it off, would ya!
Honestly,
I'm a little jealous of ya,
cause a fight with Sun
would be full of
fire and passion.
I can even imagine what
she'd say if it was me!
[KAI] I hate ya with
all my heart, Kai;
go away, ya see!
And then she'd lock me up
somewhere nice and dark,
and maybe even give me
the discipline I need!
[NAGASUMI] You're really warped.
Sun!
There's no reason
for ya to feel obligated
to that jerk Nagasumi anymore.
Call off the engagement,
ya don't have to marry him--
[AKENO] That's enough!
I've told you, think about
where you are before you speak!
Oh, Akeno!
Whoa, is somebody
getting married?
I could have
sworn I just heard
something about an engagement?
[AKENO] Oh...
Hey, look at that
over there. A banana.
[CHIMP] Oo oo ah ah!
Uhh... Is something
wrong, Akeno?
Please come with me, Sun.
[REN] "Undersea Palace
Merfolk Garden Party?"
[AKENO] It's being hosted
by Yoshiuo Minamoto.
He's specifically requested
that the Seto gang attend.
Geez! Didja hear
that, Masa?
That pain-in-the-ass
brat "requested" us!
Who is this guy, Boss?
Can I eat him?
[MASA] Actually, I hear he's
a tough pill to swallow.
If I remember right,
he's a descendent
of General Minamoto himself.
This is a direct invitation
from Lord Yoshiuo.
In addition to the Seto's,
other prominent
families have
been invited as well.
[AKENO]
He requests all solicited
to make an appearance.
Uh! Why's he want that?
Why else? So people
can kiss his butt!
I'm gettin' sick to my stomach
just thinkin' about it.
We're gonna pass.
[MASA] Boss, I understand
how you feel,
but how's it gonna
look if all the other
bosses and families
show up and we don't?
It's a matter of obligation.
We have to do our duty.
Crap, ya gotta
point there.
[REN] Ya know, Sun...
It's okay if ya
don't want to go.
No, I'll go.
[MAKI] Yay!
Just forget that
sea louse, Miss Sun!
We're gonna have
a fantastic time!
[LUNAR] We heard all
about it, manservant!
'Bout what?
Oh, just that big fight you
and Sun had yesterday!
[Lunar laughs]
[LUNAR] We didn't
think you had it in you!
We guess that old saying
"Tread on a manservant,
and it will turn" is true, huh?
[NAGASUMI] Don't you
mean "tread on a worm?"
Oh, like there's
a difference!
Anyway, we think you and us
should make a deal,
what do you say?
Huh?
You don't
talk back to us
like you did with Sun,
and we allow you
to continue to be
our manservant!
You'll spend the rest of your
life doing whatever we say!
Well, how does that sound?
Will you stop hurting
me if I say yes?
What's going on?
Oh, hi, Sun.
Don't mind me, Nagasumi.
I didn't mean to interrupt.
Just keep doin' whatever it is
you're doin' with
your love at first sight.
Sure, okay! So I guess
we'll continue then.
[NAGASUMI] No! Stop!
That tickles!
Alright then...
I'm bouncin'.
[MAKI] Miss Sun,
are ya sure it's okay if ya
don't tell the sea louse
that you're goin' to this party?
It's fine! Who cares
if he doesn't know!
I'm gonna go to this party
and cheer myself up!
Ya see, I think if
we have a little time apart,
Nagsumi'll come
around and apologize.
Oh, I almost forgot!
[SUN] I've gotta pick
some accessories!
[SUN THINKS] I can't wear
this because of the
way things are right now,
but this ring is precious to me.
'Morning, everybody.
Hey? Where's Sun?
[MOM] I was hoping that was a
question you
could answer for me.
This morning, I looked
out the window and
saw Sun leaving with
a suitcase in her hand.
[NAGASUMI] She left?
Where'd she go?
You don't know?
The reason I didn't
yell out the window
and ask her where
she was going was
because I was sure
she'd already told you.
No. She didn't.
I hardly even talked
to Sun yesterday.
[MOM] I wonder what
could have happened to
make her leave like that without
at least saying
something to you.
Hah! If you ask me,
she probably just
finally got sick
of you, manservant!
Just think: If you'd
married me,
you wouldn't be in
this situation right now!
She's gone for good, you moron!
Nah-no way.
You should have listened.
I told you to apologize
to her right away.
But you didn't, Dopey-sumi.
Well...
I'm sure she'll
be back real soon.
[NAGASUMI] Um, hey, Dad?
"I'm bouncin'" is something
they say in the Seto, right?
What's it mean?
Saying "I'm bouncin'" is
another way of saying
"Okay, I'll leave you to it," or
sometimes "Goodbye."
Is everything
okay, Nagasumi?
I forgot to mention it, but when
Sun left, Maki
went along with her.
Good morning, sweet Sun!
Hey, uh, did Sun head
to school early, Nagasumi?
[NAGASUMI] Huh? Uh, yeah.
[CHIMP] I hope
you're gonna make up
with her when you get to school!
It's no fun when
she's not around!
She's not coming today.
Wait, she's not?
How come?
No idea.
But it's certainly got
nothing to do with us.
Ask him.
[CHIMP] Well, Nagasumi?
[NAGASUMI] I don't know, either.
Um... Mr. Seto is absent
today, so I'll hand out
the printouts for
our self-guided study.
Take one and
pass it back, please.
Well, that's weird.
Sun's mom is out, too.
[MAWARI] She's not the only one!
What?
[MAWARI] Mr. Masa and Mr.
Fujishiro aren't here, either!
What gives?
Everyone who's close
to Sun is out today!
There's no way this can
just be a coincidence!
Um...
It could be.
No, I smell a case here!
My policewoman's soul is ablaze
for the first time in a while!
Uh, you're just
over-thinking this one, Mawari.
Do you have any
clue why they're gone?
Nope, but isn't school
quiet without Mr. Seto around?
Pretty nice, huh?
So nice... so funny.
[KAI] You know
somethin' about why Sun
and all the others
are missin' today.
I'm sure of it.
[AKENO] What do you mean?
[KAI] Playin' dumb
won't work on me.
Isn't it peculiar all the
Seto members are gone?
You're not
gonna talk, huh?
[phone rings]
That's fine. Kai, here.
Yeah. I see. Good work.
The Undersea Palace
Merfolk Garden Party?
And hosted by none other
than Yoshiuo Minamoto.
So I take it the Seto's
aren't here today
'cause they're attendin'
this get-together?
How did you find out?
Never underestimate
the power of the
Mikawa Conglomerate's
intelligence network.
I wonder what Yoshiuo
could want with the Setos?
[LUNAR] They're with Yoshiuo?
[AKENO] Lunar!
That's not good.
That guy's bad news.
He's pretty infamous for only
wanting one thing
from his girls.
[LUNAR] Rumor has it that really
bad things happen
at his parties.
Like what?
[LUNAR] Like people showing up
and then never being seen again.
Everyone always says to
avoid Yoshiuo at all costs.
[LUNAR] Why on earth
would the Seto gang waltz
into a party being
thrown by this maniac?
Because a gang
such as the Seto's
can't ignore a request
from mermaid nobility.
Sun's in danger!
That's why we're
sneakin' in there!
Hold on!
If you're going to defy a noble,
there will be consequences!
Ah, who cares?
Think how good we'll
look saving our rival!
You can't buy
that kind of press!
Besides, our company
is foreign-owned!
We've got nothing to fear
from Japanese nobility!
So, what's the plan?
And... Is the manservant
coming, too?
That's entirely
up to him, Lunar.
[classical music montage]
[NAGASUMI] Please be at
your dad's apartment, Sun.
[doorbell rings]
Maybe she's at home.
I hope.
Alright then.
I'm bouncin'.
[Nagasumi begins to cry]
[NAGASUMI]
Where did you go, Sun?
I'm sorry.
Please don't leave me...
With a goodbye like that.
[MAKI] What fancy digs!
I knew it'd be nice,
but this really takes the cake!
It's even bigger
than I expected.
The guy who owns
this swanky place?
You said he was a
big-shot noble, Boss?
[GOZABURO] Yeah!
Can't ya tell by
the pricy decor?
I can't stand
joints that are fulla
artsy-fartsy doodads
and knickknacks!
[MASA] Don't you find
it a bit odd that
we seem to be
the only family here?
[REN] Yes.
[SHARK]
Kinda strange, don't you think?
[slow plodding drum
that speeds up in tempo]
[ACOLYTE]
All those who are present!
Bow down!
Like Hell I'm bowin' down--
Do it!
[ACOLYTE] All hail the
mighty Lord Yoshiuo!
[CELL PHONE VOICE]
You've got mail.
[YOSHIUO] Dudes,
you're just texting me now?
[YOSHIUO] You're running late?
I've been waiting,
like, forever for this!
Jet over here so we
can get this party started!
[YOSHIUO] You dudes
are, like, total zeros!
You're un-freaking-believable
sometimes, ya know that?
Whoa, it's Sun Seto
in the flesh!
You're too hot to handle!
Lemme snap a few pix!
Say cheese sexy!
What the hell?
Get away from my daughter,
ya lecherous maggot!
Boss, take it easy!
These nobility types
can get nastier than
gangsters if they don't
get what they want!
[GOZABURO] Yeah?
Well, I can get nasty myself!
[MASA] There's no harm done,
so please settle down, Boss!
Okay?
You guys smell somethin'?
Yeah, something
that's kinda sweet?
Sun, go! Run.
You're mine, babe!
Nagasumi, help me.
[NAGASUMI] Well, Sun...
What am I supposed
to do, just give up?
[MAWARI] You look
pretty troubled.
Mawari.
You're upset, right?
No. I'm not.
I'm Mawari Zenigata,
the Demonic Disciplinary
Committee Member!
I'm all knowing and all-seeing;
you can't fool me!
It's time you
get it together!
The Nagasumi that
I know is always
honest with himself
and his feelings!
Got it!
I am?
[MAWARI] Yeah,
and if you're not honest
with yourself
right now, you'll regret it.
Yeah you're right.
How could
you say that?
Of course not.
I mean, sure, in the beginning,
I did agree to marry you because
the situation
called for it, but...
[Sun gasps]
I guess in the end,
the two of us are
just a couple for show
and nothin' else, huh?
For show?
No way.
Sun's the love of my life.
You're right. It's
time I stepped up.
And do whatever it
takes to get Sun back!
[KAI] Those are the exact words
I've been waitin' to hear!
[MECHANICAL VOICE]
We're about to surface.
Please watch your step.
[KAI] Nagasumi!
It's Kai!
This is a rescue mission!
Sun's in trouble!
[KAI] I'll fill ya in later!
Climb aboard!
Right!
Go get her, Nagasumi!
[NAGASUMI] Yeah!
So... Ya decided
to join us, huh?
[NAGASUMI] L-Lunar?
[KAI] There's no
time for chit-chat.
We've gotta get
movin' right away.
Kaiomaru!
Full speed ahead to Seto!
[sub blows horn]
[GOZABURO] What? That slimy
little rich bastard sent us
a fake invitation just
to get Sun here?
I'll kill 'em!
[MAKI] I'm gonna cut that
Yoshiuo guy up
into little pieces!
[YOSHIUO] We're gonna have
so much fun together, babe!
[Yoshiuo laughs]
[BURIO] Whoa,
check it out, guys!
A submarine, gyo!
[MAGURO] How awesome!
[AJITARO] Cool!
Bye-bye!
Hold on, Sun!
♪
[NAGASUMI] I, Nagasumi
Michishio, am more pissed off
than I've ever been
in my entire freakin' life!