Dammit, Maki,
what'd you do that for?
How the hell were you able
to dodge that attack, sea louse?
Yer response time is increasin'
way too fast way too quickly.
[MOM] Maki! Were you
able to wake up Nagasumi?
[MAKI] Yes!
I did, Mother!
That was an assassination
attempt, not waking me up!
[NAGASUMI] The new
semester starts today,
and a lot sure has changed
since summer break.
[NAGASUMI]
For one thing, this jerk
didn't used to live with us.
[NAGASUMI] But most
importantly, starting today,
Sun is going to be a
new student at my school!
Morning, Sun!
You almost ready?
[SUN] Yeah!
[NAGASUMI]
School life is sure going to
be a lot different from now on!
Good morning, Nagasumi.
This is my new uniform.
What d'ya think?
Do ya like it?
[SUN] Nagasumi?
Oh yeah, it's great!
I think it's totally
great, really!
Hey, Sun! It looks
as if your parents
have sent you a
little postcard here.
[SUN] Be right there!
[SUN] A postcard, huh?
What's that all about?
It's not too surprising.
I'm sure that your
dad's real lonely
now that you're living out here.
[NAGASUMI THINKS]
After all, he does have
an abnormal affection for you.
But what I really
want to know is how
he survived that
fall off the bullet train!
[GOZABURO]
Sun, how're ya doin'?
We've taken care
of all the paperwork
for your transfer
to that new school.
I'm sure you'll fit in real
quick, so don't ya worry.
And remember, we're always
watchin' over ya,
my precious girl!
[NAGASUMI THINKS]
Seriously? Always?
Thank you so much, Dad.
[NAGASUMI THINKS] Why don't I
have a good feeling about this?
[NARRATOR]
Beneath the gently rolling
waves of the Seto Inland Sea.
Young Nagasumi's life is saved,
and forever changed.
But as with any debt,
this one too must be repaid.
So our story begins.
Please humor them with a smile,
for young love is never easy.
♪
[SUN] So, a new school.
I wonder what
it's gonna be like.
Well, I don't really know
what to tell you about it.
It's pretty much
just a normal public
school like any
other one, I guess.
But ya see, I gotta be sure to
make a good impression today.
As yer bride,
I don't wanna cause you
any disgrace or embarrassment.
Um, yeah, Sun,
while we're on that subject,
I've been thinking.
Maybe for a little
while we should
avoid telling anyone you're my
bride or anything
about that stuff.
[SARU] Well, look who
it is! Nagasumi!
[NAGASUMI] I know
that voice. It's Chimp!
[SARU] Hey there Nagasumi!
[SARU] I love you!
You sure don't waste
time, you perverted Chimp!
[SUN] Um, Nagasumi,
can I ask ya, who is that?
[NAGASUMI] As you
can see, he's a chimp.
He's my degenerate
friend Hideyoshi Sarutobi,
but he's not someone
you need to remember.
Nagasumi, do you
really have to be so mean?
Now, who is this
incredible cutie here?
[NAGASUMI] Uh,
well, she is she's a
relative of mine,
Sun, you jerk.
[SARU] Sun Yu?
Is she Chinese?
[NAGASUMI] No, it's Sun.
Just Sun. She's Japanese.
[NAGASUMI THINKS] This has got
to be the safest explanation.
We'll be fine if
we stick to this story.
[SARU] Okay, I love Sun!
[NAGASUMI]
Just give it up already!
[NAGASUMI] Now that
I think about it, nobody told
me what class Sun
is going to be in.
Please let her end
up being in our class!
You got your wish.
Apparently she is in our class.
For real?
So...
Tell me, Nagasumi.
Wha-What do
you want to know?
I didn't get a chance
to ask you before.
What exactly is
the nature of your
relationship with
that Sun girl anyway?
Oh, well,
you see, she's, um.
Well, Nagasumi, why were
you with her yesterday?
Why did you walk to school
together this morning?
Well, it's all kind
of a long story,
you see, and I would
really appreciate it
if you could just drop it.
A secret?
Maybe I should teach you to
obey the rules of our society!
[CLASS REP] Um... Mawari
Have you heard the news?
Well, um, it seems that our
class is going to have a brand
new teacher this semester.
Really?
A new teacher?
Don't you mean
a new student?
Our information
doesn't seem to agree.
I think you've been incorrectly
informed, Class Rep.
[CLASS REP]
Oh, you really think so?
Yeah, I do...
After all, Nagasumi
and I came to school
with that lovely
new student today.
[SARU] Here she is now.
Moon, stars, and Sun!
Yeah!
Hold on that feels hard.
[GOZABURO] It is hard.
My fist is as hard as
freakin' steel, ya stupid ape!
[SARU] Look, Mom.
I can fly!
What? This can't
be happening!
It isn't fair.
[GOZABURO] All right, everybody,
sit down and listen up.
Starting today, I'm going to be
your new homeroom teacher.
The name is Gozaburo Seto.
[CLASS] The new teacher?
[NAGASUMI THINKS] S-Sun's dad
is my new homeroom teacher?
Is that what the letter
meant this morning?
[students talk excitedly]
I run this outfit now,
ya pinheads
better remember that.
I'm the new boss of
this pathetic little gang.
Any one of ya who
even things of actin' up
will catch hell that said,
it's real nice to meet ya.
But sir our teacher,
Mr. Shibasake,
--[SHIBASAKI] Hello there.
--what happened to him?
Oh... well he's on leave for...
FOR MATERNITY!
[CLASS]
He's having a baby?
All right, now
that I've introduced
myself to all
of you, let's move on.
Allow me to introduce
someone very special.
She'll be your new good friend.
You can come in now!
Oh, she's so adorable.
But, oh dear...
She does look tired.
Hi everyone,
my name's Sun Seto.
I'm from Seto Inland Sea and
it really is a
pleasure to meet ya all.
Seto?
[STUDENT A] She said "Sun Seto.
[STUDENT B] Isn't that
the teacher's name too?
[STUDENT C] He can't be.
Huh, now where should
Sun Seto's desk be?
How 'bout right here?
[NAGASUMI THINKS] This guy is
still a psycho, even in school!
Excuse me teacher,
but I think that's
enough jokin'
around for right now.
I think I'll just go ahead and
take a seat in the very back.
Sun, don't go! No!
[CLASS]
'Don't go' he says?
Hey, what exactly do you think
you're doing sittin' there?
[NAGASUMI] Well, sir.
I'm just sitting where my
desk has always been, sir.
[GOZABURO] So, maggot,
nothing's changed.
You're still a
smart-aleck, I see.
[NAGASUMI] And you seem
to be in fine health as well,
don't you sir?
[NAGASUMI]
The bell's ringing, sir.
The opening convocation
is about to start.
Do you wanna keep going?
Nagasumi, do you
know Mr. Seto?
Sun, can you please
explain this to me?
Well, Nagasumi...
It looks like Dad
became a teacher at
this school so he
can keep an eye on us.
[NAGASUMI] That means
he'll do whatever he can
to make sure
we're never alone!
Whoops,
I forgot something.
He'll need help.
[NAGASUMI] Excuse me.
[REN] Oh my,
what happened to him?
Our teacher sent him
flying across the room.
I think he's bruised
up pretty badly.
[REN] That does sound serious.
[REN] Nagasumi, get him into
that bed as quickly as possible.
[NAGASUMI] Uh-huh.
[NAGASUMI THINKS] How does
she know my name?
You're lookin' well.
Nice to see ya again.
Hey, wait a second,
you're Sun's mom!
Ya just dropped your
little monkey-like friend.
Is he gonna be alright?
This is great!
I thought it was just gonna be
her dad spying on me,
but now her mom's here
in some doctor coat!
Oh, do ya like it?
Thanks, that's sweet.
I must say, my husband
didn't care much for it.
I wasn't trying
to say anything like that!
I just meant that this is all
getting absolutely crazy!
[REN] Yes, you may be right.
Perhaps it is a bit crazy
to call in a favor with the
Ministry of Education in order
to work as school personnel.
[REN] But you know
what, Nagasumi?
Sometimes just
goin' a little bit crazy
can make life a whole
lot more interestin'.
[NAGASUMI] So what
are you doing here?
[REN] Now that ya
know about us mermaids
and you and Sun are engaged,
you need to become
one of us, don't ya think?
[REN] And if you don't think
our little Sun is enough for ya.
Perhaps I could make
you into my own kept man.
[NAGASUMI]
What are you talking about?
I need to get out of here!
Excuse me! I gotta go!
[REN] He's so cute!
[NAGASUMI] I can't
believe Sun's mom
has actually shown up here too!
This isn't even remotely funny!
But she did look really nice and
she smelled so very sweet.
No, Nagasumi!
Stop it right now.
This is crazy!
Damn it, these people are
really trying to ruin my life!
Why can't...
Wait just a second.
Is that--?
[NAGASUMI] It's Masa!
That's right...
I'm glad to see that
--[VOICES] ...a fated reunion.
--you're still hangin' in there.
I've come to assume a new
position as a math teacher, see.
So I'm sure I'll,
see you around.
Yes.
I'm sure we will--
No, what I really
wanted to say was,
how many of the Seto gang have
come to this school, anyway?
This ain't good.
That bastard Nakajima really
screwed up his
anthropomorphosis.
Nakajima?
[NAGASUMI] Yeah...
He's really messed this one up,
and it looks like one of
his legs has been cut, too.
Well at least the opening
convocation's already
gotten under way.
Lucky for you guys.
Of course right now
I'm just surprised
that you all haven't
been found out already.
[SHARK] Oh, if it
isn't Nagasumi?
Idiot!
Why the hell you bitin'
at him, Shark Fujishiro?
[NAGASUMI] Wait,
he said "Shark Fujishiro."
Does he mean--?
[SHARK] Haven't you
figured it out yet?
If this human dies,
then we all get to go
home to Seto, right?
So we really don't
need to worry, huh?
[SHARK] I won't leave
a shred behind?
[SHARK] I'm the PE teacher,
Shark Fujishiro?
I look forward to
teaching you, Nagasumi?
[NAGASUMI] Well, I don't!
[SHARK] The convocation's
already started?
I'll kill you while there
aren't any witnesses?
[NAGASUMI] This is seriously
getting worse by the second!
Half the teachers are
from the Seto syndicate.
Not good!
[SUN] Stop it, Fujishiro!
[NAGASUMI]
Oh, hey, Sun, thank you!
Oh that was
Howling Voice,
it's a mermaid techniques.
I wanna know what
exactly's goin' on here.
I went to check
on you in the
nurse's office,
and my mom was there.
[REN] Ya sure found
us out quickly, dear.
[SUN] And Dad's workin' here
as my homeroom teacher.
[GOZABURO] What's all
the fuss about over here?
[SUN] And Masa's here and
Fujishiro and Nakajima!
And then when
I opened my bag
I saw that Maki'd come
along with me too.
[NAGASUMI] So that
creature is here too?
[NAGASUMI THINKS]
This is unbelievable!
These people are going too far!
They're completely
taking over my school!
I've had it with them!
Sun needs to give 'em
all a good talking to!
Now, all of ya all of ya.
Ya have my utmost thanks!
[SUN] I'm so lucky to
have this many people
looking after me and
worryin' about me.
[NAGASUMI] And so
the Seto gang turned
up to look after their dear Sun.
They showed up in full force.
That's how my school year began.
[GOZABURO] We'll always be
watching over her, don't ya see?
[Nagasumi crying]
[NAGASUMI] It's horrible!
I can't believe it!
How could Sun's dad actually be
posing as a new
teacher at my school?
Now I'm going to have to see
his ugly face every single day!
[NAGASUMI] Sun, I don't know if
I want to go to school anymore!
[NAGASUMI] Oh it's Sun.
Sun's right there smiling at me!
[NAGASUMI] Sun!
[MASA] Oh, you on your
way home, Nagasumi?
[NAGASUMI] I know
that voice! It's Masa!
[NAGASUMI]
What fantastic timing.
I feel so lost right now.
Maybe I'll just give up and
leave everything in his hands.
[MASA] What are
you talking about now?
[NAGASUMI] At this point,
I honestly have no idea.
[MASA] So that's it, then?
The boss's paternal
affection for
Miss Sun is grindin' ya down?
[NAGASUMI] That's about it.
I mean, he did become a teacher
in order to come after her.
That just isn't normal.
And are you all
right with this?
Of course I'm not all right!
No, that isn't
what I meant.
What I was asking was,
if you're ready to
forfeit this battle.
Are you willing to accept
that you may care
for Sun less than
her father cares for her?
[NAGASUMI] Masa.
[NAGASUMI] You're right.
I can't lose this battle.
Sun's already
sacrificed too much
for me to give up like that.
I'm going home now, Masa.
I'll see you tomorrow at school!
[NAGASUMI THINKS] I'll
show Sun I care for her
as much as her dad does.
No, even better,
I'll become a man
who she'll really fall for.
[NAGASUMI] I'm gonna
give this my all!
[SARU] Sun! Are you ready?
[SARU] Let's get going!
So you're not here to walk
to school with me, then, huh?
Well, that kick of yours
wasn't half bad, Nagasumi.
But would you like to explain
why you're attacking me?
Listen very closely
to me, Chimp.
Sun is a special person,
and she is extremely
important to me.
I owe her my life.
No one can care about
her as much as I do.
You get me?
Oh yeah.
I get you.
Then you'd better make
sure you stay away!
What's with the threatening
and yelling all of a sudden?
[NAGASUMI] I've decided to live
a macho life, starting today.
You can just go live
in the mountains
like the chimp you are!
So you're suddenly
macho, are you?
Sure am.
[SARU] Then let me ask
you something, Nagasumi.
What's that sticking
out of your bag?
[SARU] Because it sure
looks like a doll to me!
[NAGASUMI] Maki!
What're you doing?
You know you're not supposed
to let humans see you!
[MAKI] Isn't it
obvious, sea louse?
I'm pretendin' ta be a doll.
Don't ya think that
getting' so worked
up talkin' to a doll
like this makes ya
look a little crazy, though?
Nagasumi, I don't
know what happened
to you over summer vacation,
but I can't believe that
you're into dolls now!
[NAGASUMI] N-n-n-no, wait!
[SARU] Well good luck to you.
Hope you enjoy the rest
of your life with your doll.
You're wrecking my new
macho life in the first minute!
[MAKI] Yeah, you can
handle that yourself.
Dammit,
I'm not going to lose!
I'll beat her dad and make
him acknowledge me as
a man if it's the last
--[SUN] Mornin'!
--thing I do in my life!
The road to manhood
is a difficult one!
[MAKI] Whatever,
just go to school.
Okay, since all of ya
brats are new to me.
We're gonna start off
with a kanji test right now.
Are ya ready, huh?
[NAGASUMI THINKS]
I'm pretty good at Kanji tests.
This is my chance
to impress her dad!
[NAGASUMI] All right, Sun!
Watch this!
[SUN]
'Kay.
[GOZABURO] Okay, it's time
to check your answers.
First up. Code of honor.
The next
one is a bit tougher:
"Manly chivalry." The next
one is written "territory,"--
[NAGASUMI THINKS]
This is ridiculous.
I'm gonna forget
about impressing him.
[MASA] Listen up,
this'll be on the test.
If your monthly
action from Territory A,
newly controlled by you,
is two parts tribute money,
two parts rent, and three
parts protection money,
and you want to make
ten mil a month--
Mr. Masa's lectures are
so easy to understand!
They ARE, but
somehow I feel I
shouldn't get too deeply
involved in the subject matter.
Tell me this is not
what I'm thinking!
So far there have been
no opportunities to show off.
[SARU] Psst, Nagasumi!
Over here!
[NAGASUMI] Hmm? Chimp,
what are you doing there?
You'll get yelled at for
going out there, you know.
Never mind, come on.
You see. It's
a perfect view.
From here you can peep at all
the girls while
they're changing.
Hey no, Chimp, there
will be no peeping!
[SARU] What the heck, Nagasumi?
I thought you were going to
act like a man from now on!
[NAGASUMI] Like a man?
Hey, this is acting
like an animal,
not acting like a man!
Not that I'm entirely
uninterested in it.
Just get over
it, Nagasumi.
While girls are changing,
boys are peeping at them.
That's how it is.
In what country
is that the way it is?
[SARU] Nagasumi,
just think about it a minute!
If they didn't want us
to peep, why would they
be changing behind
one measly curtain!
The girls actually want us to
look at them, don't you see?!
No! No,
is that really true?
You won't fool me like that.
I'm not that stupid,
monkey balls.
Why don't we
be honest with
ourselves for a
minute, Nagasumi?
On the other
side of that curtain,
paradise is waiting for us.
What are you saying, exactly?
[NAGASUMI] Pa-Paradise?
What do ya say, kid?
Don't you wanna
find happiness together?
It'll feel real nice,
I promise you that.
[NAGASUMI] Happiness?
We could find happiness
in that shining paradise!
No, no, no, no.
If I'm not careful,
I'll be dragged
into Old Man
Chimp's letchosphere!
I will not lose this battle,
no matter what.
I am determined to live
a manly, macho life!
Damn, kid, you're
some kinda idiot.
Or is it that you're
more interested in
your little dolls than
in real live babes?
Is that it, little girl?
Don't make
fun of dolls, okay?
On second thought, drop
that subject completely!
[SHARK] Hey, you over there?
[SHARK] Who said
you could go out there?
Oh, no.
This is really bad.
Come on, Chimp.
[ANSWERING MACINE (SARU)]
I can't come to the phone now.
[NAGASUMI] Damn you,
Monkey Balls.
[SHARK] Well, well,
who is that? Is it Nagasumi?
[NAGASUMI] Oh no,
I recognize that speech pattern.
It's Shark Fujishiro!
No, I'm afraid that
name won't do here boy?
I'm the PE teacher
here, after all.
So it's Mr. Fujishiro to you.
He jumped up
to the second floor?
I'm so screwed.
This guy might actually be more
dangerous than Sun's father!
[SHARK] You're a
stupid boy, Nagasumi?
Letting me find you alone
in a deserted place like this?
You know what I'll do?
I'll eat you?
In under five seconds?
[SHARK] I'll bite off
your head and eat it?
[NAGASUMI] Just let
me go and I'll never eat
another bowl of shark
fin soup again, I swear!
Please!
Hey, is there something
going on out there?
This is bad!
I've hit a dead end!
[SHARK] Oh good!
Time for lu--
[NAGASUMI] I don't
want to be shark food!
How am I supposed
to get out of this?
I could dive into
that classroom.
But no, right now they're--Argh!
Sun, what do I do?
I don't want to be swallowed
whole by this man-eating shark!
It's all over now!
My life is over!
What was I supposed to do?
Arrest him!
Detain Nagasumi on
charges of molestation
and the public display of
obscene materials!
Do it now!
Now!
[GIRLS] Yeah, arrest him!
Arrest Nagasumi now!
[CLASS REP] Mawari, you should
at least put your shirt on.
[MAWARI] Well,
you've done it now.
You really crossed a
line today, Nagasumi.
[MAWARI] What could
you have been thinking,
barging into the girls'
changing room like that?
It was completely idiotic.
And I was in the
middle of changing
my clothes, I hope you know.
[MAWARI] Maybe
I should teach you
a lesson in the
rules of this society.
[NAGASUMI] Officer Mawari,
I understand that you
smoothed things
over with the teacher.
Thank you so much.
But, uh...
It's all my fault in the end.
It doesn't matter anymore.
A person like me has no right
even attempting to be macho.
[NAGASUMI] I can't
explain to her about Fujishiro.
I'll never tell anyone about
the secret of Sun's race.
She saved my life,
so I owe her that.
I hope that pervy
chimp dies, though.
[NAGASUMI]
What good is any of this?
Oh, Sun.
I don't want to go to school
anymore, I'm sorry!
[NAGASUMI] Oh its Sun!
Sun is smiling at me!
Just wait, I'll be right there!
[SUN] Did ya just call
my name, Nagasumi?
[NAGASUMI] Oh, Sun.
What are ya doin' out
here on the bridge all alone?
[NAGASUMI] Um, well.
[NAGASUMI THINKS] She told
she had some things to take
care of and I should
head home without her,
but she probably was just too
embarrassed to
walk home with me.
Now I've even
lost Sun's trust.
What are you doing, Nagasumi?
[SUN] I'm real sorry, Nagasumi.
I couldn't manage
to prove your innocence,
but I tried real hard,
I promise.
[SUN] I even asked Chimp
to help, but he wouldn't.
I swear on my honor I tried my
best to get you off the hook.
[SUN] In the end,
I guess I'm a
failure as a bride.
[SUN] Class Rep and
Officer Mawari were
eventually able to get
everybody under control.
[SUN] I was really sweatin' in
front of Officer Mawari though.
She makes me nervous.
Really, you can
just call her Mawari.
[SUN] But anyway,
everything's going
to be okay now, you'll see.
So then, you aren't...
You mean you aren't
mad at me or anything?
[SUN] What for?
Well after what I did,
I thought that you would be.
I'm sure that ya
had a reason, right?
I believe in ya, Nagasumi,
and today doesn't change that.
Ya see, if I didn't believe in
my husband, then it would
be a disgrace to all Seto
mermaids everywhere.
Ya see, because honor among
thieves' is
'honor under the seas.'
Thank you, Sun.
Understand now?
I'm yer bride,
Nagasumi, and there's
nothin' that's
gonna change that.
[NAGASUMI THINKS]
I don't think my heart's
ever felt like this before.
An engagement that's merely
the product of the
law of the mermaids.
A love that doesn't come
until after the engagement.
But the feeling
I have right now has
nothing to do with
laws or sacrifices.
It's pure, and simple,
and quite real.
[SUN] Come on, let's go home.
[NAGASUMI] Yeah...
[NAGASUMI] Okay, Sun,
I think you understand
this already, but...
Right, our weddin'
is a secret.
I'll be careful not
to tell anyone,
so ya don't have to worry.
Hey, guys,
what's going on?
Let me in on all
the fun here, will ya?
Shut up, traitor!
Why don't you just
go eat a banana
like the pervy
chimp that you are?
We are sorry, but ya
see, it's our little secret.
What?
[NAGASUMI] Right?
[SUN] Right!
They're in
their own world!
Why are they
alienating me like this?
[GOZABURO] A secret, huh?
Ya got a secret,
you little maggot?
That's no good Nagasumi,
no good at all ya fappy bastard!
Ya might wanna
rethink that, in fact!
[GOZABURO]
"Our little secret," my ass!
[NAGASUMI] So this is how
things are gonna end again?
[SUN] Dad, stop it!
Let him go!
♪
[NAGASUMI] It sure
seems that Mawari's
been lashing out a lot lately.
After Maki, I don't need any
more violent women in my life.
Huh?
Mawari's suspicious of Sun?
This is bad!
This is really bad!
Wait, I can unveil my sure
fire technique:
Nagasumi Barrier.
It's gonna be great!