[SUN] Thank you, Mother,
and thank you father.
Thank you for always lookin'
after me for all of these years.
Now I, Sun Seto, now I am--
[NARRATOR]
Beneath the gently rolling
waves of the Seto Inland Sea.
Young Nagasumi's life is saved,
and forever changed.
But as with any debt,
this one too must be repaid.
So our story begins.
Please humor them with a smile,
for young love is never easy.
♪
[TV HOST]
Now Lunar, you're still in
junior high, isn't that right?
[LUNAR] Yes.
It must be rather
tough for you to
balance your studies along
with a big singing career.
Yes, it is, but you
can't be a pop star
unless you're willing
to do a balancing act.
Did you hear
that, everybody?
Isn't this little girl
really something?
Wow, Lunar, on television,
you're a hundred times
cuter than in real life.
What you meant to
say was that in real life,
we're a million times cuter
than we are on television.
[NAGASUMI] Yeah, of
course that's what I meant.
[LUNAR] Hand us
that remote, Nagasumi.
[NAGASUMI THINKS]
Her fans are lucky
that they never
have to see this.
[MOM] ♪ I love doing
the dishes with my ♪
♪ daughter in my
sparkling kitchen! ♪
♪ What a wonderful way to
spend a lazy Sunday afternoon! ♪
Ya seem like you're havin'
a whole lot of fun, Mother.
Of course I'm happy.
Why wouldn't I be?
I feel like one of my lifelong
dreams has finally come true.
I've wanted a daughter for
as long as I can remember.
Thank you so much.
Just hearin' ya say that makes
me feel happy too, ya see.
I mean sons really
are no good, are they?
Hearing that
doesn't make me happy.
[MOM] I admit I was
devastated when
our house was destroyed, but...
I guess it turned
out all right since
Lunar's father is in the
construction business.
You can say that again!
The most modern
kitchen available,
and with all electric
appliances, too!
Only the very best!
I don't know what
you're so excited about.
At our estate, all of this stuff
would be handled by servants.
Ya've got it
all wrong, Lunar.
That isn't the point.
[LUNAR]
What's the point?
Ya see, this is part
of my bridal trainin'.
Training?
I'm marryin' into a
dry-land family, after all.
So I have to learn to do all the
work Mother does
around the house.
[MOM] What a fine bride she is.
Too bad she's wasted
on the men of my family.
What an old
fashioned attitude.
Those ideals are tres passé.
I dunno what language
yer speakin',
but man is a ship and
woman is his harbor.
See Lunar, it's a wife's
duty to protect the home.
You're behind the times.
Are you sure you were
born in the nineties?
Now, now girls, there
is no reason for fighting.
It's okay...
you can disagree.
Come on Sun, it's time
to go shopping for dinner.
Okay!
We've got to give today's
meal all the effort we've got!
Yeah!
Hey Lunar, do you
wanna come with us?
[LUNAR] No,
I sure don't.
Wonder why not.
Lunar's probably
tired from working
so hard singing
and going to school.
Oh I see, so Lunar's
a ship instead of a harbor.
[MOM] Look after the
place while we're gone!
[LUNAR] Yeah, yeah.
[TV HOST] I understand you
have a new album coming out?
[NAGASUMI] Seriously, Lunar.
You should've gone
shopping with them.
Why didn't you
just drop the act?
Drop what act?
[NAGASUMI] Wasn't it one?
[LUNAR] Of course
it wasn't an act.
Quit trying to pretend like
you actually know something,
manservant,
and learn your place.
My crotch is in some
serious trouble here!
Well, never
mind all that now.
'Cause you see...
We're finally alone
in an empty house.
How can you talk to
me all sweet and cute
like that and give me the
Grinder at the same time?
[LUNAR] I was just thinking...
We live together, but we've
never been all
alone before, right?
I've been waiting
for this moment.
Well, that's a shock!
[NAGASUMI] Lunar seems to be
radiating this incredible charm.
But why? What does
she want to do?
Why does she want to be alone?
Want to go
up to my room?
Up the stairs
to adulthood.
[DAD] I can't tell you
how upsetting it was
when our house was
destroyed last week.
Thanks for your
help fixing it up.
It was no problemo.
It gave ya an excuse
to see yer daughter,
didn't it, Edomae?
So I bet from your end it
was all fer the best, huh?
You can just visit.
You don't need a
complicated excuse for it.
I said no problemo.
Ya can see how much of
a pain in the ass this guy is.
He loves his daughter,
but he's got no social skills.
Oh yeah, like
you're one to talk.
What?
Ah! Uh, nothing, nothing!
Well here we are, finally
alone, so now you can...
Lunar!
Tutor me, Nagasumi!
It's much better
for it to remain this way.
I know it is.
Yes, really.
Quit mumbling
and start tutoring me.
We gotta make this quick!
Yes, of course Lunar.
You know, if you
really do need help
with your schoolwork,
Sun's grades
are better than mine are.
Us? Being tutored by
that airheaded space cadet?
Really? We'd rather die than
be humiliated in such a way.
Honestly, we'd rather die!
Did you have
to say it twice?
Sun's a moron
who writes all her
answers one line off from
where they're supposed to be.
And then gets confused
when somehow,
there's an extra
question at the end!
[SUN] Hmm?
Yeah, Lunar may
have a point there.
Aside from which,
we don't want Sun
to know we're having
trouble in school.
That's unacceptable!
She's such
a prima donna.
Now hurry up and help us
study before Sun gets back!
Oh yeah, a total
prima donna.
You'll earn penalty points
every time you talk back to us!
Okay, so go ahead
and do it! Bring it on!
Yeah?
You wanna piece of me?
'Kay, let's go!
[LUNAR] Oh yeah!
[NAGASUMI] I'm losing
my grip! I can't take it!
Tutor us and the
Grinder will stop.
Why do you care so much
about your studies, anyway?
Trust us.
This isn't exactly how
we wanted things either.
[LUNAR] You see,
the teacher said...
Miss Edomae, this is turning
into a serious problem.
Oh, come on. A pop star
doesn't really need math.
Maybe not, but it isn't
just math in this case.
You've gotten
zeros on everything.
It's unbelievable.
Are you collecting
them or something?
That's just mean!
We basically
steamrolled these
people into letting
us be teachers here.
At the very least
we have to give the
appearance of doing
our jobs correctly.
So what are you saying?
I'm telling you
this as a teacher.
If you don't
improve soon,
then I'm afraid you'll
have to, repeat the year!
NO!
[VOICES] Flunk out!
But I'm only
in middle school!
[MASA] No one ever
said life was fair.
Oh, you're having
study trouble?
Maybe I can help
tutor you if you want.
H-Hi, Zenigata.
That isn't a bad idea,
Miss Edomae.
"Miss"?
Uh, what I mean is,
maybe you should
take Zenigata up on that offer.
Oh, yeah sure.
[LUNAR THINKS] No way!
We can't ask this
wannabe cop to tutor us.
That would be humiliating!
[LUNAR] Oh, thank you so
much for the offer, really.
But all I have to do is
go back to my estate,
and there will be a whole team
of experts waiting to tutor me.
[MASA THINKS] Right. If she
had even one tutor at home,
she wouldn't be
getting grades like this.
Come to think of it, Lunar.
You mentioned
your estate just now,
but I don't think I know
where you're living.
Well, I keep it a secret,
since I'm a celebrity.
Oh, I see.
Between the paparazzi
and the stalkers,
it's a lot to have to deal with.
I hadn't realized how difficult
it is being a big star.
You're right about that.
It can be rough.
And as a result,
I've ended up neglecting
my studies for the first time.
I'm always mentally
and physically
exhausted from my
hectic celebrity's schedule.
Stress is the
illness of our age.
Our little spaceship
called Earth is in trouble.
I think you
lost me somewhere
around the spaceship
part of that speech.
But anyway, we're
classmates, so you can feel
free to come to me with
any problem you have.
Oh! Thanks so much,
you're so sweet!
It means a lot to me to know
that I have a friend on my side.
[Lunar spits]
[LUNAR THINKS] Just saying
this stuff makes us sick!
You live in a much different
world than us, girl!
And don't you forget it!
But again, I really do
appreciate the offer, I mean it!
Thank you so much!
[MAWARI] Sure.
Well! I'll see
you later! Okay!
Lunar has such a lovely
smile, don't you think so?
[Masa groans]
What's the point
in calling food 'lovely'?
I can go ahead
and eat you now?
You keep up that harassment.
I'll have you arrested!
Okay, I get it.
Why should
someone like us
be forced to repeat
a grade in junior high?
This is a major
pain in the ass,
and we have to put
up with it because they
think that they can
measure a superstar,
by the same standards
as common people.
Compulsory education,
nothing you can do about it.
It's gotta be nice
to be so carefree.
Hey, I am not carefree.
I'm stuck tutoring a prima donna
who doesn't get
anything but zeros.
You're pissing me off.
Be more respectful!
You like this?
All right, here's more!
[NAGASUMI] I can never go back!
I can never go back!
[NAGASUMI] She bit
the hand that fed her.
Damn you manservant.
[NAGASUMI] Solve this by
memorizing the formula.
It's easy as that.
Wow, you're right.
You know, you're a
surprisingly good teacher
for someone who
doesn't get good grades.
It kinda helps that we're
still on the easiest part here.
Whatever. Just get
on to the next part.
Could you sit
somewhere else?
Please, You're kinda heavy.
We are not heavy at all!
Now, would you be a good
chair and quit complaining?
Wait, now she's
treating me like furniture.
Hurry up and start
teaching us the next part.
Um, yeah, okay.
My...
Lunar, what is it?
Us sitting here is making
you a little bit hot, isn't it?
You were a big
fan of Lunar the pop star
long before you
met us in person,
isn't that right?
So, is this your fantasy?
You're beloved star
sitting here on your lap?
No, no of course it isn't.
[LUNAR] We're just going
to shift a bit. Don't mind us.
[NAGASUMI THINKS]
With her sitting there,
I'm losing my grip
on a lot of things.
And my heart
won't stop pounding!
A manservant shouldn't
have the hots for his master.
But it's certainly entertaining.
[NAGASUMI THINKS]
Come to think of it,
I was Lunar's fan
long before I met Sun.
I was Lunar's fan first!
[NAGASUMI] No, I can't!
I can't do this, Lunar.
My loyalty belongs
to Sun, not to you.
Yes, that's right,
you are Sun's.
So why are you getting
the hots for us, then?
Really. You shouldn't
be doing something like this,
now should you?
Lu-Lunar, let's try
and stick to studying, okay?
[LUNAR] You have to pick
between one or the other.
Your marriage to Sun or
your place as our manservant.
Which is it?
I don't think that
I have to pick.
It seems I already have both.
There's only one
answer that we'll accept.
You're ours, Nagasumi.
Go on! Just do it! Do it!
Come on, ya know
that ya want to.
[clicks with each head movement]
[Nagasumi and Lunar cry out]
Oh, hi, Maki.
I didn't realize that
you were sitting there.
So nice to see you.
Lovely weather we're having.
Don't mind me.
Just keep on doing whatever
it was you were doing.
Huh? I don't know what you
are talking about, Maki.
Ooh! Ooh,
you were about to kiss.
You were gonna do
all kinds of things.
Admit it, sea louse.
Ya know ya wanna tell me.
Like hell I do!
[MAKI] I'll have to
report this to Miss Sun.
Oh, please don't do that!
I beg you!
No, go ahead, Maybe
it'll all be for the best.
No, it certainly
would not!
[MAKI] And of course
I can't forget to report
that Miss Lunar got
zeros on everything.
You can't do
that to us, Maki!
[MAKI] All that groveling
looks like hard work.
It's makin' me kinda thirsty.
Oh, of course! I'll get
you a drink right away!
What is it?
[MAKI] Miss Lunar.
[MAKI] Miss Lunar...
Ya don't seem to think too
badly of the sea louse.
Do ya think?
Would ya mind hookin'
up with him a little bit?
What the heck? Where did
that idea come from?
Where'd it come from?
I've never seen someone
flirt that much with
someone who they didn't
like at least a little bit.
As if we'd ever fall for a
member of the human species!
There's no way!
[NAGASUMI] Here,
I brought that drink.
Oh, hey,
sea louse. Listen up.
You're never
going to believe this.
Miss Lunar told me--
[LUNAR] Why you!
Take that!
[NAGASUMI] Wait,
what's going on here?
I don't understand,
but please don't stop it!
[MAKI] Basically it's
a choice between
marriage to Sun and
becomin' Lunar's servant.
[MAKI] As long as this
rat becomes one of us
sea folk one way or
another, it's all good.
Everyone can live.
If the Edomae could just take
the sea louse off our hands,
then he wouldn't
hafta marry Miss Sun.
He can be Miss Lunar's
manservant,
and that would solve everything.
[NAGASUMI AND LUNAR]
You quit butting in, Maki!
Why can't the two
of you just hook up, huh?
How can you suggest it?
We'd never date a human!
Ever since
Sun saved my life,
I swore that I'd give our
relationship all I've got.
And I meant that for life.
I don't care what it solves!
I'd never date stupid Lunar!
[LUNAR] What are
you talking about?
Are you saying that we
aren't as good as Sun?
Lunar, what the heck
do you even want?
[MAKI] I knew it!
You two are perfect!
Perfect for each other!
Shut up already!
[MAKI] What's the
matter, sea louse?
You're her fan, aren't you?
Why can't ya hook up with her?
What's the big deal here?
How can you even say
that with a straight face?
Anyway, forget it.
What I feel for Sun
goes way beyond that.
Sun Seto's the only one for me!
Then I guess
there's no choice.
If there's nothin'
Miss Edomae can do
to change your mind, sea louse.
I'll just have to
seduce you myself.
[LUNAR THINKS]
Is this shrimp actually
saying she's sexier than us?
Take a look
at this, sea louse.
Is it sexy?
Is this what you like to see?
In the end, all men
are beasts, after all.
Shut up and put
that away, Maki!
[LUNAR] Manservant,
from now on you love only us.
That's an order!
You got it?
We'll take good care of you
as long as you obey us, okay?
You understand?
[NAGASUMI] I have no idea
what's going on anymore!
Miss Lunar, in the end
you're exactly like Miss Sun.
The two of you are
still nothin' but kids.
Ya lose yer human form after
the tiniest splash of water.
I can't hold on!
There you go, turning into
your mermaid form again.
Here's a towel to dry off.
[MAKI THINKS] Always
so quick to wipe off
a girl's legs, huh, sea louse!
You're my manservant,
aren't you?
Dry me off! Dry me off now!
Hey now, what's wrong?
Even if I am
a successful singer,
I always lose to
Sun! I'm a terrible student,
and even my manservant
thinks Sun is better than me!
I'm completely pathetic!
[NAGASUMI]
Like hell you're pathetic!
You aren't pathetic at all,
Lunar! Think about it!
You do mountains of
homework every day.
But I've never
done my homework.
You stay up until
midnight reading scripts,
and then you go into work
at five o'clock in the morning.
[NAGASUMI] And then
you show up at school.
You have a tough
time studying because
you're working as hard
as physically possible.
I won't let anybody get away
with calling you pathetic.
Not even you yourself!
[NAGASUMI] After all. I like
you, and don't you forget it.
But not as much
as you like Sun.
Oh, well. that may
be true, but Sun is--
Hurry it up! Come over
here and dry off our legs.
It's a manservant's
duty, after all.
[NAGASUMI] Uh, right.
[MAKI THINKS] You're
really workin' on that
manly honor,
aren't ya, sea louse?
I wonder how I should
report this to Miss Sun now.
[tires screaching]
[DAD] Again, I'm
truly grateful to you
Mr. Edomae for arranging
the construction,
and to you Mr. Seto for
paying for it, of course.
I only paid for the repairs.
I left your original thirty-year
mortgage as it stood.
You understand that?
For a wealthy mob man,
you certainly know
how to be a tight-ass.
Oh, nothing!
[LUNAR PAPA] Lunar.
[DAD] Oh! Mr. Edomae,
would you like to see Lunar?
I'm sure she's in her room.
All right, Lunar.
How's this?
Yeah, just like that.
A little more.
[NAGASUMI] Here?
[LUNAR] Yeah, right there.
[Lunar giggles shyly]
[NAGASUMI] Huh?
Lunar.
[NAGASUMI] Um, sir.
It's not how it looks.
[LUNAR PAPA] That's it for you,
human. You're terminated.
[NAGASUMI] Her legs were wet.
I was just drying them off.
That's all, Dad!
[LUNAR PAPA] Who are you
calling 'Dad?' Terminate!
Quit being so
overprotective, Papa!
I'm going to drown
this human in the bay.
[VOICES] Ker-splash!
Don't you dare!
[SUN] Oh, it looks like Dad
and the others beat us home.
[SUN] What's going here?
[MOM] Yeah, could
someone explain?
[GOZABURO] Hello, Sun.
You've got excellent timing.
But, we need to talk.
What? How can this be?
Nagasumi cheated on me?
And it was with Lunar?
I believed in Nagasumi
up until now, my dear.
I really did.
I kept telling myself
that Nagasumi was a guy.
A guy I could trust with
the welfare of my only daughter.
But!
Our trust has now been
betrayed by this monster!
It's hard, I know.
It's difficult for me too,
but yer relationship
with him is over.
[Gozaburo starts to laugh]
Nagasumi?
[MOM] I only took my eyes
off him for one second.
It was an unfortunate
accident, dear.
Let's forget
about Nagasumi.
You can't forget about me!
I'm your precious only son!
Yes I need
a chopper ASAP.
There's a human
I need to drown.
[LUNAR] Papa!
Lunar?
Stop right now.
Leave Nagasumi alone!
Lunar. Just what else
am I supposed to do?
I caught him
touching your butt.
You're blowing
this out of proportion.
Our butt's no big deal!
What?
You touched her butt?
No, this is a
misunderstanding!
Nagasumi says
it's a misunderstandin'
You can't believe a
word that this maggot says!
Have the courage
to face the truth.
Reality is harsh.
Nagasumi, rest in peace!
Lunar are you
trying to tell me that
you love this human
is that the situation?
Oh come on...
Us, love a pathetic
human like him?
After all, I like you,
and don't you forget it.
[LUNAR] Y-Yes...
We love him, so you
leave him alone, Papa!
[LUNAR PAPA] Human.
You can either take
responsibility, or die.
[LUNAR PAPA] Responsibility.
Responsibility.
You'll marry Lunar or die.
What? Marry Lunar?
--[DAD] Already? At his age?
--[MOM] No. Engaged twice?
Yeah, good for
you, Naughty-sumi!
Really, Lunar?
Well, Sun. Yeah.
Th-That's right!
Nagasumi has to learn to take
responsibility for his actions.
[Lunar fake laughs]
I'll go ahead and take
your son with me right now.
Mr. and Mrs. Michishio,
I'll send someone
to get you when
we're ready to perform
the ceremony. Got it?
[MOM AND DAD] Uh yes!
Hold on, Edomae!
I've got somethin' that
I need to say to ya!
Good job!
Nagasumi!
No, Sun, stop it.
Let Nagasumi go.
Here, drink this.
Hey, thanks!
--[both laugh]
--[NAGASUMI] You're so tense.
[GOZABURO] You're good at that!
I'm afraid Nagasumi
isn't with us anymore!
I'm right here?
Nagasumi, come back!
I'm sorry!
Get goin' already,
you maggot.
[LUNAR] We're going.
Nagasumi!
[SARU] La la la la!
[SARU] Hey, a helicopter.
My lord, look.
There's a helicopter over there.
[KAI] Whoa look at 'er go!
[KAI AND SARU] Hey!
[NAGASUMI] Chimp! Mikawa!
Hurry you guys, help!
Woo-hoo! We got to see a
helicopter today. How cool!
[NAGASUMI] Morons!
I think that this is probably
all for the best, Miss Sun.
Once you go back
to the Seto Sea,
you'll forget about
him in no time.
I won't though.
[SUN] I can't help but feel
like part of this is my fault.
Ya see, maybe
if I'd been a better
bride ta be, this wouldn't
have happened.
But what can I do about it now?
[SUN] Huh, Maki? What do I do?
[Nagasumi cries out]
Please, Lunar...
Damn it. This is all a
misunderstanding, Sun!
[NAGASUMI] Help, Sun!
♪
[NAGASUMI]
I've sure got a lot of life
experience for someone my age!
I'm engaged for the
second time against my will.
No, I'm telling you...
Sun is my true bride!
But now an all-out brawl between
the yakuza families
is unavoidable.
I must sacrifice my
life to accomplish...
What would that
accomplish, exactly?