[DAD THINKS] Damn it.
I'm doing the best I can,
I really am.
[horns honking]
[HENCHMAN] Damn it.
[SECRETARY] Damn it!
[gunshot and then gun click]
[tires screaching]
[machine gun fire]
[SECRETARY] Hey boss!
Come back!
[sirens]
[DAD] Wha-what's-?
[LUNAR PAPA] Target.
Lock on.
[NARRATOR] Beneath
the gently rolling
waves of the Seto Inland Sea.
Young Nagasumi's life is saved,
and forever changed.
But as with any debt,
this one too must be repaid.
So our story begins.
Please humor them with a smile,
for young love is never easy.
[alarm rings]
[NAGASUMI]
Lunar no. Please stop.
Just a dream. Oh, good.
What a weird dream.
That was some nightma--
Listen up human.
If you do not treat my Lunar
with the proper respect,
you will find yourself
terminated quickly.
[NAGASUMI THINKS]
He. he. he. He's not a dream!
[Magasumi cries out]
[banging around]
What's wrong?
Are you okay Nagasumi?
You look like you're
really freaked.
Sun, just now there
was a man in my room.
A man in your room?
Yeah. Big.
[NAGASUMI THINKS] Wait a
second. The weird guy said
something about
Lunar, didn't he?
Hey Sun, where's
Lunar right now?
Lunar ran outta the house
in a panic just
a little while ago.
All she said was that she had to
do some work again this morning.
[NAGASUMI] Oh. Okay, I see.
[NAGASUMI THINKS] What the heck
was that all about, anyway?
Heya Nagasumi.
Incredibly normal
morning, isn't it?
Yeah, thanks for
stating the obvious
for no apparent reason, Chimp.
It's just that lately,
every morning's brought
some fun new
drama along with it.
So now I'm feeling
a little deflated.
Do you think that
you could go
and deflate somewhere
else, maybe?
He's right, though.
It has been lively lately.
[SUN] First Kai
transferred to the school.
And then there was field day.
And don't forget
that amazing singing
contest between you and Lunar!
It was hot!
Again Chimp,
could you reminisce
somewhere else, maybe?
Exactly, there's
nothing to get so
excited about, ya damn monkey.
I'm sick an' tired of this
outta the ordinary stuff.
[NAGASUMI THINKS]
Out of the ordinary!
[MAWARI] Seriously now, Chimp!
Why can't normal, everyday
events be enough for you?
Yeah, Chimp,
normal, everyday events
are much better in the long run.
Whistle! Whistle!
Now you're getting
on my case, too, huh?
It does seem
like you've been
actin' pretty
strange all mornin'.
So you've finally
lost it, Nagasumi?
That's fantastic news.
[NAGASUMI THINKS]
It's pretty hard not to tell
anyone about
something this weird.
Maybe I should let
these guys in on it.
I was worried about
saying anything
because they might
think I'm nuts,
but they're my friends, right?
If I just act natural enough,
I'm sure they'll
be very accepting.
Yeah, I'll do that.
I'm sure they'll be
behind me 100%.
Well, actually.
When I woke up,
a strange, gleaming,
six and a half foot tall man
dressed all in black
was standing by my bed with
a shotgun and
threatening to kill me.
And then he jumped
right out the window.
Surprising, huh?
[NAGASUMI THINKS] Oh boy.
Your room is in the attic
above the second floor.
You do realize that,
don't you, Nagasumi?
You don't believe me?
He was really there, I swear!
And you're the only
one who's actually
seen this supposed man?
I wasn't hallucinating!
Um, Nagasumi...
Maybe you should go
home and rest a little bit.
[NAGASUMI] I'm not sick either!
This is my fault.
If only I'd tried harder
to counsel you when
you so obviously
needed some help.
I don't need a shrink!
[NAGASUMI] Come on Sun, please,
tell me you saw that!
SUN] Huh?
What now?
[NAGASUMI] Are you blind?
The gleaming man
in black showed up again.
He was right there!
Here, right here!
He fogged up the
window with his breath
and wrote 'Lunar is
my life' with his finger!
[SARU] Dude,
there's nothing there.
Oh. Well, it must've dried
up and disappeared.
[NAGASUMI] And he did it again!
He left with an
amazing backward jump.
Just like this!
[MAWARI] We're on
the second floor.
[NAGASUMI] Don't you
think I know that?
I don't have a clue what
he wants either, but...
No, wait! Wait!
Don't leave me behind!
I'm telling the truth!
Please don't leave!
[SHARK] Well now,
we certainly can't have this?
Trespassing on
school grounds is strictly
forbidden and quite
closely monitored?
And bringing something
as dangerous and
deadly as that
shotgun you have there
into a student area
is definitely a bad idea?
Your track suit,
you'll give it to me, now.
[Shark chuckles]
[SHARK] It looks like I'm
wasting my breath on you?
I guess I'll have no choice but
to remove you
by force then, huh?
[REN] A strange man, you say?
Yeah, but no one
will believe what I say,
and I can't figure out
how to convince them.
But it is the truth! Really!
I saw him
with my own eyes.
A man who's six
and a half feet tall?]
That's right.
A man dressed
all in black,
carrying a shotgun,
whose body gleams?
That's right.
All right then, maybe
you should lie down and rest.
I'm telling you, it's true!
Please listen to me!
But it's true. I saw it.
Oh! It's not fair!
Why won't anyone
believe what I'm saying?
[Ren sighs]
A strange man
dressed all in black, huh?
[REN] All in black?
[Shark cries and sniffles]
[clock ticks]
[NAGASUMI] Oh, is that the time?
I must have fallen asleep.
It seems like it's
unusually quiet in here.
[NAGASUMI] Hey, uh, Sun's mom,
are you here somewhere?
Well, she's not answering.
I guess no one's here then, huh?
[NAGASUMI 'Kay, I guess I'll
just go back to the classroo--
[Nagasumi cries out]
[NAGASUMI]
Sun's mom turned into that
strange man wearing
a gym jersey!
[NAGASUMI]
Kai Mikawa! Perfect timing!
Nagasumi Michishio.
Blah, blah, blah, et cetera.
Let me guess.
You're being chased
by a gleaming,
six and a half foot tall
man dressed all in black,
carrying a shotgun,
who's wearin' a
jersey now for some reason?
Come on, don't you think
you should let this one go now?
[NAGASUMI] It's true! I'm
telling the truth! Just look!
Huh?
Where did he go?
[KAI] Hah.
Why don't you save
your dreamin' for bedtime.
He was definitely
there a second ago!
My goodness, yer
a mighty nervous type,
aren't ya Nagasumi?
Do yourself a favor and try
to copy my refinement
and dignity.
[NAGASUMI AND KAI] It's him!
[KAI] Nagasumi,
who the hell is that
six and a half foot tall,
gleaming man carrying a shot gun
and wearing a skintight
jersey for some reason?
[NAGASUMI]
That's what I'd like to know!
He's still coming after us!
[KAI] We've gotta
get out of here now!
[KAI] No! The outside!
[NAGASUMI] Do you
have to do that right now?
[SARU] My lord Kai!
[SARU] Here my lord.
[KAI] What is it Chimp?
[KAI] Oh yeah!
[SARU] Please, take this.
[KAI] Well done Chimp...
I'll give ya a banana later.
[NAGASUMI]
You're so high maintenance.
My lord, good fortune to you.
[KAI] Who the hell is that guy,
and why is he chasing us?
How am I supposed to know?
But we're inside now.
Can't you take that
stupid thing off already?
When I'm ready.
Hey do you think.
That maybe he gave up?
[NAGASUMI AND KAI]
This statue's kinda warm.
[KAI AND NAGASUMI]
Total! Recall!
[KAI] How much longer is
this guy gonna chase us?
[NAGASUMI] And how
does he keep making
it to places before we do?
[NAGASUMI] Oh, that's
not good! It's a dead end!
[NAGASUMI] He's getting closer!
[SARU] My lord Kai!
Grab on tightly to
the rope, my lord!
[KAI] Chimp!
Okay Chimp, I'm ready.
[NAGASUMI] NO!
What're you doin',
Nagasumi Michishio?
[NAGASUMI]
You think I'm going to let
you escape all
by yourself, you jerk?
[KAI] Jus' do the right thing
and sacrifice yourself for me.
[SARU] If you keep struggling...
[NAGASUMI] You'd make
a more appropriate
sacrifice than me, I think.
[KAI] Let me go or I'll
kick you in your fat face.
[SARU] Can't hold
it much longer.
[NAGASUMI AND KAI] Chimp! No!
[NAGASUMI AND KAI] Chimp no!
Why is this happening to us?
I don't understand.
It's obviously all your
fault, ya dirty bastard!
Shut up! This is
exactly why the only
friend you have
is all your money!
Quit shoutin he'll find us
because of your stupid face!
[KAI] Oh, please spare me!
[NAGASUMI] This is
the end of us, isn't it?
[KAI] Of all the people to share
my last moments on Earth with.
[NAGASUMI]
Just what I was thinking.
[NAGASUMI] Oh, Sun!
[KAI] Oh, Chimp!
Did the guy, go away?
Are--
Are we safe now?
[KAI AND NAGASUMI] Yea!
We're both still alive!
[KAI] He broke
a hole in the wall!
[NAGASUMI] And now
I bet he's still--I knew it!
He's right there!
[KAI] All right, if that's
how this is gonna go!
[NAGASUMI]
Why do you even have a
thing like that
in the first place?
[KAI] For self-defense.
[NAGASUMI]
Whoa! He actually did it!
[alarm bells ring]
[KAI] I did it!
I got the guy good!
I always knew I had
that killer instinct in me.
Never mind the method
as long as we're safe now.
[KAI] Don't underestimate the
Mikawa family,
ya freak of nature!
He's been blown
ta smithereens!
I've got a taste
of violence now,
and ya know, I like it!
Ya' I do!
Just don't ever use that
thing on me, okay, Mikawa?
[GOZABURO]
All right, ya little punks.
Form yerselves into a line.
[GOZABURO] Word from the top
is we're evacuatin' to the gym.
Apparently the first floor
is some kinda disaster area.
That's strange.
I wonder what that
explosion could've been.
Come to think of it,
there was that gas
explosion not long ago.
I'll need to make a thorough
investigation into both of them.
Hey have ya seen
Nagasumi anywhere?
He did go to the nurse's
office earlier this morning.
That's a long time for
him to be there, though.
[school bell rings]
I can't believe that I'll never
get to eat miso katsu again!
[KAI] Or Doteni stew!
[KAI] I woulda liked a miso
katsu parfait for my last meal.
[NAGASUMI] Farewell, Kai.
[NAGASUMI THINKS]
He'll come after me
no matter how far I run.
Oh, Sun. I'm afraid
it's all over now.
[SUN] An' what do
ya think yer doin?
You're the guy, the one
Nagasumi told us about.
I'm not gonna
let ya hurt him.
Nagasumi's my husband,
and ya won't harm
a hair on his head.
'Cuz, honor among thieves...
...Is honor under the seas.
Uh, Sun!
Sun Seto.
Ultranso--
[NAGASUMI THINKS] He prevented
her from using Howling Voice?
How does he know how
to fight mermaids like that?
Hey you!
Let go of Sun right now!
[SUN] Nagasumi!
[GOZABURO] I'll kill ya!
[GOZABURO] That's my daughter.
What do ya think yer doing?
You filthy piece of shit!
Oh Dad, you saved us!
[NAGASUMI]
Did Sun's dad really save me?
[GOZABURO] I'm gonna give ya
a beatin' ya won't soon forget!
[GOZABURO]
Take that! And that!
How do ya like that, huh?
Dad seems really angry.
He's totally flipping out.
Seriously, this is crazy.
Sure that guy's an
invincible monster,
but at this rate even he--
[GOZABURO]
Not the urinal!
[SUN] Oh no, Dad!
[NAGASUMI] He beat
your dad? Impossible!
Human.
You are living with Lunar.
What exactly are your
intentions toward her?
Huh?
What about Lunar?
[NAGASUMI THINKS]
Come to think of it,
he said something
like that this morning.
Answer me now human.
[NAGASUMI THINKS] I'd better
answer. He's not messing around.
Where Lunar's concerned,
you're asking the wrong person.
You see.
Lunar came to live
with us because of Sun.
I'm not talking
to Miss Seto now.
I'm asking you what your
intentions are toward
her, puny human.
I don't understand
what you mean by that.
I don't know--
[SUN] Dad, you're okay!
[GOZABURO] This ain't over!
Did ya really think
ya had me beat?
[GOZABURO]
This time I'll kill you!
You can beat that guy, Dad.
Get 'em, okay!
My Sun!
Now time to die!
Is that all
ya got, Edomae?
Edomae?
Oh, I guess it is him.
[SUN] I've met that man before.
Are you sure you're not
the one losing your
touch in your old age.
Gozaburo Seto?
I'm gonna pulverize ya!
[NAGASUMI] This is crazy!
[Gozaburo cries out]
[GOZABURO]
Ya useless, filthy rat.
It's about time for you to meet
your ugly end, Edomae!
Good luck, Dad.
This fight of theirs is really
starting to get out of control.
At this rate, they
might both die.
This'll be the
final blow for you!
[LUNAR PAPA] Die!
Stop it now!
Dad please stop this!
[LUNAR PAPA]
I'll let you off easy,
Gozaburo Seto,
but only this time.
[GOZABURO] Yer just lucky
that I let ya survive, Edomae.
Oh, thank goodness.
Sun, can you please
tell me who that guy is?
Who is he?
Uh, well, Ya see.
[LUNAR] Hey, what the heck
are you doing at the school?
[NAGASUMI] Lunar?
[SUN] And my mom?
My, my, my.
Seems we missed it.
Lunar.
Tell me why
you're here, Papa
[NAGASUMI] Huh? You mean
that guy is Lunar's father?
Which also makes him the
boss of the Edomae gang?
[SUN] Uh, yeah. I'm real
sorry about that, Nagasumi.
I totally forget that
I'd met him before,
it was at the
yakuza get together.
[NAGASUMI]
It'd be really great if you
could remember
these things sooner.
[SUN] I was super
surprised when I figured
it out durin' their fight.
Well,
you gonna answer me?
[LUNAR PAPA] I had
business with the school.
I'm going home now.
[helicopter blades rotating]
[SECRETARY (M)] There
you are, President Edomae!
I've been looking for
you everywhere today.
I'm glad I found you.
You've missed several
important business meetings.
I wonder what
kind of business
Lunar's dad had
at the school.
If I had to guess,
I'd say he probably
came around to see
what kind of man he
had entrusted his beloved
daughter's welfare to.
His social skills are
as clumsy as ever.
[SECRETARY] Huh?
President Edomae! Wait, sir!
Where are you going?
Hasta la vista Baby.
[NAGASUMI] Wait! How's he
going home through there?
Jeez. That man.
He can be very difficult
to have as a father.
[Lunar Papa's henchmen
begging him to come back]
[NAGASUMI] I don't think
'difficult' would be the
word I would use
to describe that guy.
[HENCHMEN]
President Edomae!
♪
[VOICES] Masa Today!
[music playing]
[PROPRIETRESS] Hello, welcome.
[door closes]
[MASA] So you decided
to come, after all.
I didn't expect you to show.
[MASA] You seem to
be doing much better.
I think this calls for
a celebratory drink.
[MASA] Owner.
Let's have one of the
usual if you don't mind.
[PROPRIETRESS] Sure.
[MASA] Here we are.
The Liquid Shot.
It's a house specialty.
[MASA] At any rate,
that was a close call.
Why didn't you say
something to us sooner?
Things almost go out of hand.
We might've taken out a
couple of hundred people
before it was all
said and done.
And at that point,
clipping some fingers
and apologizing
wouldn't have cut it.
[MASA] Perhaps,
it was a matter of pride?
It isn't that
big of a deal.
Sometimes it's fine
to come crying to us.
Don't you know?
Please, don't
give me that crap.
Do you take me for
some yellow-bellied fool?
Miss Sun doesn't
like me anymore!
She's been actin' so distant
ever since that
thing with Lunar!
She won't even let
me out of this cage.
I'm trapped in here like a rat.
It's the boss who
ordered that cage.
It has nothing to
do with Miss Sun.
I can't live
with this anymore!
I'd rather kill myself than
have Miss Sun hate me!
[MAKI] Masa!
Take the plunge with me!
[MASA] Where did
you get that thing?
[MAKI] Miss Sun.
I'll be watching over ya from
heaven as long as yer alive.
[MASA] Maki, stop it!
[PROPRIETRESS] Excuse me, sir.
--[MAKI] Hey!
--[MASA] Owner?
[MAKI] What're ya doin'.
Where are ya takin' me?
[water splashes
and toilet flushes]
[Maki cries out]
[MAKI] Masa!
[MASA] Maki! Maki!
[NAGASUMI] Spending money
is fun, right everybody?
It's easy to find
yourself buying away
from tv programs
or internet stores.
Wait, why is the Seto gang
running a tv shopping program?
Well, it's an honest
business, at least,
and I think that's wonderful.
Once again, I take a
hit for the home team!
My home is Earth!