[FISH BROTHERS] Gyo, gyo,
gyo, gyo, gyo, gyo, gyo, gyo,
Gyo, gyo, gyo, gyo,
gyo, gyo, gyo, gyo,
gyo, gyo, gyo.
Gyo!
[AKENO] So this school is
my target for this mission, eh?
My, how vexing.
[NARRATOR] Several dozen leagues
from the Inland Sea's foam.
Lies the land of Saitama,
birthplace and home.
But where'er you go,
the demons still roam.
A violent mob's on the scene.
Watching the
schoolboy's routine.
And poor Nagasumi
is only fourteen.
Like a stormy sea, the course of
this love is
anything but smooth.
♪
[CHIMP] Hey, Nagasumi?
You know that ghost story
that's going around school?
Huh?
Ghost story?
Really? You mean
you haven't heard?
People have been
seeing half-fish,
half-man monsters here at night!
Half-fish,
half-man, huh?
Great, it could
only be THEM.
Are you scared,
Nagasumi?
Scared enough to pee your pants?
You wanna diaper,
you fraidy cat?
No, I'm not scared,
Chimp, just appalled.
[GOZABURO] Alright,
look alive, punks!
Everybody's here today, right?
It doesn't matter.
We gotta new transfer student
who's gonna be joinin' us.
You can come in now.
[Students "oooand ahh"]
My name is Akeno Shiranui.
It's a pleasure to meet you.
[NAGASUMI THINKS] There
sure are getting to be a lot
of transfer students
in this class.
Is that a katana? It is.
"She appears
quite humanlike.
But...
So... Miss Akeno,
there's an empty desk
in the very back row over there.
[GOZABURO] Let's get started.
I'm pleased
to meet you, Akeno.
[VOICES]
Pop star on the job!
[AKENO] Likewise, Lunar Edomae.
Oh, wow!
Well then, I guess you've
already figured out our,
I mean, my true identity!
[AKENO] I may not know
much about this world,
but even I have heard of Lunar,
the world-famous pop star.
Wow, I bet you're really
surprised to find
us here, aren't you?
You're probably wondering why a
pop star is attending
a public school!
Well...
I am a bit curious.
What are you doing at
a school in Saitama?
Poor simple Sun
just can't do without us,
so we came here for her sake.
Aren't we just the
greatest friend that
an unimportant girl
could ever have?
[AKENO] Hmm... So you came
here for Sun's sake, eh?
[CLASS REP] Well, Akeno...
Do you have all the textbooks
you'll need for class?
No...
Actually I don't yet.
You see, my transfer
was pretty sudden.
Oh... Well, if that's
the case, ya can share
books with me
if ya'd like to.
Is that all right?
Since we're gonna
be neighbors.
I'm more than happy to.
Thanks...
That's very kind of you
to offer to share, Sun.
[Lunar laughs heartily]
[LUNAR] Is that what you
call kindness, one book?
Come on, that's nothing!
[SUN] Lunar?
Here, Akeno, please! Use mine
instead! It's better!
Besides I'm a star!
Anything for a true fan!
Thanks,
but Sun's already
offered and you
need one yourself--
It's fine!
Don't worry about me!
You can have 'em all!
[SUN] Hey, Lunar.
How 'bout showing me
a little respect, okay?
If I took back a book
I already loaned out,
what kind of friend would I be?
[SUN] Are ya even
listening to me?
[LUNAR] A pop star
needs her beauty sleep!
[SUN] I see.
"It appears these
two are not normal. Huh."
[NAGASUMI] Akeno seems like she
could be a pleasant person,
but she definitely
comes across as a little,
well, gruff, I guess.
You don't agree?
[CHIMP] This is
exactly why you're still
wet behind the ears, Nagasumi!
Uh! He's returned!
The Pervy Hermit!
[CHIMP] Nagasumi,
you nincompoop!
How dare you get my
name wrong, dad blast it!
Address me as Chimp Roshi!
[NAGASUMI] Roshi!
That girl...
Though she might appear to be
serious and stone-faced,
don't be fooled.
I peg her as someone with a
wealth of hidden
pretty-girl power!
P-Pretty girl power?
[CHIMP] Chimp Eyes activate!
[CHIMP] Pretty-girl power
value eight hundred thousand,
eight hundred
and fifty thousand,
nine hundred thousand!
She's in the same
class as Sun and Lunar!
That's impossible!
[CHIMP] But, wait!
Look at her boobies! Perfect!
[CHIMP] The size!
The volume! The curves!
She might even
be hotter than Sun!
Akeno's no mere
junior high student!
She's a goddess!
What did the heavens put
her on this Earth to do,
that they gave
her so much power?
Just looking at this
vision of womanhood
is pushing me into
meltdown mode!
And my cooling rod
won't cool down at all!
Oh, I can't
take it anymore!
Everyone, please!
Raise up your hands up!
Send me your energy, now!
[NAGASUMI] Like anyone
would give any to you!
Ape face!
And you are?
[NAGASUMI] Oh, we
haven't been introduced
yet thanks to
all that commotion.
I'm sorry 'bout that.
Pay it no mind.
This class is always like that.
I'm Nagasumi Michishio.
Nice to meet you.
[AKENO] Nagasumi, huh?
I've heard of you.
[NAGASUMI] Huh?
From what
someone told me,
you're close to
Sun and Lunar, right?
Uh...
Did Mr. Seto say that?
I'm sure it was him.
What's your relationship
with them?
Well, they, um, uh...
They're staying at my place.
Just for certain reasons,
of course!
[AKENO] And just what
would those reasons be?
Uh... Well, I guess, you could
say they're distant relatives.
Yeah, that's it!
Ah... "Relatives."
Right, so a lie,
very well then...
Whatever it takes
to maintain the
secret from outsiders, I guess.
[NAGASUMI] Huh?
[KAI] Hiya, Akeno.
[KAI] That's a nice-looking
sword you got there.
If ya ever need
a sparrin' partner,
Believe it or not, I know a
little bit 'bout swords myself.
[AKENO]
"Kai Mikawa...
Heir to the
Mikawa Conglomerate...
...of the Chukyo
Industrial Zone."
According to this,
you're very wealthy.
[KAI] Well, now, I'm mighty
impressed there, Miss.
You're not just pretty,
but smart, too.
Explain something Kai...
What brought someone
like you to this school?
Simple...
It was for love!
I came for my one and only.
He's Sun's stalker.
That's why he came here.
What?
You've got some nerve!
Where do you get
off insulting my pure love,
you pathetic,
no-good human scum?
I didn't say anything
that wasn't true!
Alright Nagasumi,
that tears it!
I'm gonna teach you about
the power of the merfolk!
Fine! Bring it on,
you Sea World reject!
[MAWARI] Stop it!
No fighting in here, you two!
Maybe I should teach you
the rules of this classroom!
You fail! Kai!
[KAI] Feels, so darn, good.
Whoa... She
knocked him out.
[AKENO] Kai Mikawa fails.
How vexing.
[SUN] Failed what?
What are ya talking about?
Here, look at this.
[SUN] Wait, is this?
[AKENO] He said
"No good human scum,"
and "power of the merfolk."
But...
The use of such
phrases in front
of humans is inexcusable.
So is flaunting the power
of our kind to humans.
It demonstrates
a flaw, so he fails.
You said "Our kind?" Akeno,
are ya saying you're a--
Correct...
I'm the same as you,
Lunar, and Mikawa.
A mermaid.
[SUN] Ya said Kai failed.
What did ya mean
by that exactly?
[AKENO] Those who
fail the exam must
leave the human
world forever.
I'm the official
who passes
judgment over those who take it.
[AKENO] Kai Mikawa's
being returned to the sea.
--[KAI] Chimp. Please. Help.
--[SUN] What?
Kai's gonna get
sent back to the sea?
And you will too if
you don't pass the exam.
I've already discussed
this with your father.
With my father?
[GOZABURO THINKS]
Just hang in there, Sun!
[AKENO] I've also instructed
Maki the Conch to stay
at home for the
duration of the exam.
[AKENO] She won't be
joining you at school today.
I'm so sorry, Boss!
I feel so pathetic
not bein' able to
help you out when
you're in trouble!
And I can't stop cryin'!
And just how
the hell did I end
up getting stuck
in this package?
[MAKI] Oh, no! The beast!
The beast is comin'! Stop!
Don't come any closer!
I don't wanna get hurt again!
Just get away from me,
ya mangy furball!
I'm not a snack!
Nooooo!
[AKENO] There's no
one here who can
help you with the exam, Sun.
[AKENO] Naturally,
you're not to tell anyone.
If you do,
you automatically fail.
Revealing my true
identity to those I test
is always the first
part of the exam.
Wait... Ya mean?
[AKENO] Yes, Akeno Shiranui's
Mermaid Exam has already begun.
It's a test to
determine if you'll be
allowed to remain in the human
world or sent back home.
[SUN] Mermaid Exam?
[OCTOPUS NAKAJIMA]
Lately, I've been hooked
on patchwork, mostly quilts.
Listen up, 'cause
this will be on the test.
Let's say you have one
cheap punk and ten bosses.
You gotta multiply
by four the formula
for the probability
of the punk completing...
That's useful info! Isn't
Mr. Masa just the greatest?
[NAGASUMI THINKS] Yeah,
both in terms of looks
and giving us a great education
in underworld accounting!
[AKENO] Masa,
lieutenant of the Seto outfit.
Based on my observations,
there don't appear
to be any issues with him.
I'm sure you figured this out,
but you're not the only one
that I came here to test, Sun.
And know this...
If one of the others slips up,
revealing themselves
as mermaids to the
human population.
I'll fail them
on the spot as well.
[SUN] And if ya fail, ya get
deported back to the sea!
I gotta pass!
If I don't, I'll get
sent back to the
Seto and Nagasumi'll
be left here all alone!
Um...
Hey, Sun?
Yes, Nagasumi,
what do you want?
I won't leave you!
Ms. Sun...
Are you okay girl?
Who? Me?
I'm great. Why do you ask?
For one... Your
book's upside down.
[SUN] It is?
About time you noticed.
You're taking notes
on me? Oh, no!
Hey, I don't get it.
Why did Akeno knock me out?
[CHIMP] My lord...
What is it, Chimp?
Would ya just hurry
and help me up?
Look over
there, my lord.
[KAI] Sun! She's staring at
me with such compassion!
[KAI] She's never looked
at me like that before!
Wait! Could
this finally mean...?
My guess, my lord?
Her heart started to
flutter wildly with sorrow
when she saw you laid
out on the floor in pain.
Fluttered? Oh, Sun!
[SUN THINKS] Oh no,
Kai failed and now he's
gonna have to go back
to the sea forever!
Goodbye, Kai, it's been
real nice knowing ya!
Please take care of
yourself and keep in touch!
Don't worry your pretty,
little head, Sun...
You look like you
lost a friend or something.
[KAI] Come here
and I'll make it all better.
[KAI THINKS] At last...
This long-awaited
moment has finally come.
Oh, Sun, I'm gonna
hug you so tight, I--
[Sun cries out]
[CHIMP THINKS] What a klutz!
[SUN] Owie ow!
[Sun screams]
[SUN] No, please
don't write that down!
[AKENO] "She has a
psychologically fragile side."
How vexing.
Well, class haha. Today...
We're gonna add a drop of
liquid B to liquid A okay?
[insane laughter]
Be real careful!
You don't wanna lose a hand?
[NAGASUMI] Agghh! Oh crap,
you put in too much!
[NAGASUMI] Wh-What the...?
[MAWARI]
Something's smoking! Run!
[CLASS REP]
Everybody, duck and cover!
[DYNAMITE GINJI] Yes! At last!
It's finally here!
[insane laughter]
[MAWARI] Property damage...
Improper handling
of hazardous materials,
maybe I should teach--
[AKENO] Forget the exam.
I feel like Sun Seto might
be a lost cause anyway.
How vexing.
[NAGASUMI] Akeno!
[AKENO] Yes, Nagasumi?
Sun's acting really
strange today.
You just met, but do
you have any idea why?
I'm afraid I don't.
The best thing to do would
be to ask Sun directly.
[Sun sobs]
This isn't a good day.
[NAGASUMI] Oh, so this
is where you ran off to.
Hi there Nagasumi.
You've been acting
really funny today, Sun.
Is something bothering you?
--[SUN] Oh, no!
--[NAGASUMI] Uh, Sun...?
Not you! You're so cruel!
And you're twisted!
Me? I am?
What did I do?
No! Just wait!
Ya got it wrong!
Got what wrong?
Sun I...
Oh please! Have mercy!
What? But I haven't
done anything!
Please! I'm begging ya!
[SUN] I'll do anything
ya ask of me!
Just please don't
do that, I'm begging!
Sun! What's going on?
How vexing.
[CHIMP] Oh!
Over there in the
distance, my lord!
Busty Akeno!
And not just Akeno,
but Akeno in gym clothes!
[CHIMP] They're jiggling!
[CHIMP] Bouncy bouncy!
[CHIMP] Jiggly jiggly!
[CHIMP] I can't take it!
I'm heading into
meltdown mode again!
[KAI] You fool...!
I've already got
my heart set on Sun!
That new girl might
be busty and all but...
But I guess it's okay if
look and don't touch, right?
Of course, my lord!
Don't feel ashamed!
All we're doing is
following our instinct to
cherish and admire
something beautiful!
It's the natural bounciness
and jiggling of life!
It's not perverted at all!
[KAI] Really?
Hey, you're right, Chimp!
We can't go against
our natural instinct,
so I say we follow it!
[KAI] Forgive me, Sun!
[KAI] My eyes! My eyes! My eyes!
[CHIMP] Just remember to
think happy thoughts, my lord!
[NAGASUMI] Could you guys
just go somewhere else?
I'm worried about Sun.
She's still not looking good.
I wonder what's
gotten into her today.
[SHARK] Nagasumi?
What might you be doing over
here away from all the others?
Skipping out on
my gym class are you?
And here you are, scoping out
the girls in their gym clothes?
No sir! But, those
two are certa--
[CHIMP] Go Isono! Fight!
[KAI] Oh!
[CHIMP] Fight!
[NAGASUMI]
That's just great...
Those two are pulling
this stunt once again?
[SHARK] You've sure got
guts lying to me, Nagasumi?
It looks like you really do
need to be taught a lesson?
A painful one?
Could you just
give me a break
and the benefit of the doubt
this one time, pretty please?
[SHARK] Not a chance?
[SUN] Fujishiro, no, stop!
Please don't do that!
No, there's nothing
to see over there!
Um, Sun,
are you alright?
[LUNAR] Hang in there,
Sun! I'm here!
[AKENO] Uh...
Hah! We'd rather of
smacked you right in the
face with our fist
instead of a dodgeball!
[LUNAR] You poor thing!
That looked really painful!
Your face is swollen!
Although not enough
for our tastes!
Consider this payback
for showing us up
in front of Akeno, you
damn Goody Two Shoes!
Hold on! I'll go to the
Nurse's office and get
Ms. Ren as fast as I can!
Ha! Like hell we will!
You can just stay here and
eat dirt for the
rest of the day!
[AKENO] That girl's like a pot
of negative emotions, isn't she?
Um, Akeno? Does this
make me a failure?
As a mermaid, no...
As a human, yes.
Don't let it get you down.
[SUN'S SOUL] Mama! Mama!
Mama! Mama! Mama! Mama!
Your soul is
slowly escaping.
Hey um, Sun...?
Yes, Nagasumi?
I couldn't help but notice
you're acting really weird.
Whatever it is
that's bothering you,
you can talk to me about it.
[SUN THINKS] I promised
Akeno I wouldn't
tell anyone about the exam.
I can't even talk to Nagasumi
about what's going on.
[NAGASUMI] Sun, what's wrong?
Thank ya, but I can
handle it on my own.
I really appreciate ya worrying
about my well bein', though.
Ya see... I'm gonna do
my best to protect
our life the way
it is right now!
Just watch me!
Yeah, but...
Don't worry
about me, 'kay?
'cause everything's gonna be
alright soon, I'm sure of it.
Ya hear me, Nagasumi?
Okay but... I...
I don't know why,
but if you insist.
then I'll respect
your wishes, Sun,
but please listen, don't push
yourself too hard, 'kay?
Okay... I promise I won't.
Thanks, Nagasumi.
I was certain you
were going to give up.
I thought you were going to
crack and tell him everything.
I gave ya my word
that I wouldn't tell.
It seems a person's
true nature shines
through in the end,
whether it's good or not.
Hey, where's our dinner
lousy manservant, hurry up.
Just behave as
your usual self.
And try not to get nervous.
Yeah... you're right.
Departin' from my everyday self.
Well, that just went against
our kind's code of honor.
From this moment forward,
I'm back to bein'
the usual Sun Seto!
[VOICES] The Usual!
[SUN] Uh!
What the...?
[KAI] My eyes! My eyes!
Um... Akeno! What the
heck are you doing?
[AKENO] Nagasumi,
wipe off Sun's legs!
What?
[AKENO] And don't worry...
I won't let anyone
into this classroom!
[BURIO] Not if we have
anything to say about it!
Oh no, it's THEM!
[BOY E] The terrifying
trio that scared all
the other gangs in
school into submission,
even though those guys
are only second-year students!
[BURIO] Burio!
[AJITARO] Ajitaro!
[MAGURO] Maguro!
[FISH BROTHERS] The
toughest at Isono Junior High:
the Branchial Respiration Three!
You're about to find out why!
[AJITARO] Right, it's time we
paid you back for last night!
[AKENO] You all fail at trying
to hide your true selves!
[KAI] Not bad, but let me show
ya show some real moves.
[AKENO] You again, Kai?
Like I told ya before, I know a
little something 'bout swords!
[KAI] So allow me to
demonstrate the greatest
merman sword technique
of the marine world!
[AKENO] You fail again!
[KAI] My eyes! My eyes! My eyes!
[GOZABURO] Hey, ya
little wastes of space!
Why aren't you in class?
Just what the hell's goin' on?
[BOY A] That's the toughest
person at Isono Junior High!
[BOY B] Gozaburo the
Japanese Teacher!
Mr. Seto...
Round up these
students, would you?
[GOZABURO] Alright, kids.
It's time we all got
back to class now.
[STUDENTS] You take
orders from Akeno?
[FISH BROTHERS]
It sure sounds like it! Gyo.
[SUN] Oh! Akeno!
Hey look, my legs
are back to normal!
[AKENO] Sun Seto!
You dunce! You fail!
[BOY F] That sword's real!
[BOY G] Holy cow!
[NAGASUMI THINKS] I know
I've seen this before,
but when Sun has a sword,
she becomes a
totally different person!
You moron!
I told you to be careful.
But instead of listening,
you screwed up again!
[AKENO] Not listening
is going to cost you!
[SUN] So then...
I guess I failed, didn't I?
[NAGASUMI] Sun?
[SUN] I'm sorry.
I tried my best, I really did,
but she says I fail.
Huh? What do you
mean by "fail?"
Hey, Nagasumi?
I know it's a lot to ask,
but would ya come
live with me in Seto?
[NAGASUMI] Huh?
Um... Akeno. Tell me...
How much longer will
I be allowed to stay here?
Hold on, both of you.
What did Sun fail?
And what does she
mean "living in Seto"?
Once I report this to all
the agencies who are involved,
you should be transferred
within one week.
Wait, transferred?
[SUN] A week? That's it?
[AKENO] However...
Much to my
shock and surprise,
I was unable to land
the blow of failure upon you.
That's the first
time that's happened.
[AKENO] Therefore I've
decided to defer this "fail"
until the day I do
manage to land that blow.
You're safe for now.
I am, really?
[AKENO] I just hope
that you've learned today
that you need to
apply yourself more.
[AKENO] Good answer.
I have high hopes for you, Sun.
Thanks, Akeno!
So what was
that about exactly?
[STUDENTS] Now Akeno's the
toughest at Isono Junior High!
[STUDENTS] Tough-est!
Tough-est! Tough-est! Tough-est!
[NARRATOR] As of lunch
break on her first day here,
Akeno Shiranui conquers
Isono Eighth Junior High!
[AKENO THINKS] How vexing.
[NARRATOR]
Her Mermaid Exam continues!
[KAI] My eyes! My eyes! My eyes!
♪
[NAGASUMI] Akeno might be
a Mermaid Exam administrator,
but she's also earned
the rep of being the
toughest person at school
on her first day here!
It's sparked a
big war and everyone's
talking with their fists
instead of their mouths!
Our youth has been stolen
by violence and chaos!
The gangs are on the warpath,
and Akeno's the
one calling the shots!