Don't trust a stranger,
and assume they don't trust you.
[MAWARI (YOUNG)]
This one's mine!
[NAGASUMI (YOUNG)]
Nagasumi barrier!
Ow, ow that hurt.
Nagasumi that isn't fair!
My Nagasumi Barrier.
The next one is:
aim to be better.
[NAGASUMI (YOUNG)]
This one's mine!
[MAWARI (YOUNG)]
No way, it's mine!
I can't let you have this card.
Mawari, that's not fair.
Play by the rules.
This is my favorite card
out of all of them.
I can't ever let anyone else
have it, no matter what.
I can see why, Mawari.
That card's basically your
life's goal in a nutshell.
Yes, absolutely.
I know that someday,
I'm gonna be a great
Superintendent General,
just like my dad!
[NARRATOR]
Beneath the gently rolling
waves of the Seto Inland Sea.
Young Nagasumi's life is saved,
and forever changed.
But as with any debt,
this one too must be repaid.
So our story begins.
Please humor them with a smile,
for young love is never easy.
♪
Good morning, dear.
Uh, honey?
[MOM] Yeah?
[DAD] Oh nothing.
I was just dreaming a bit.
[MOM] About what?
[DAD] About us.
You and I were
living in a house of
our own complete with
a thirty year mortgage.
[MOM] A nice, steady,
grown-up life, huh?
[Mom laughs]
That doesn't exactly
sound like you.
[DAD] You never know.
People do change after all.
Maybe it will sound
like me someday.
You're sounding like
an old man are you okay?
[Dad chuckles]
[DAD] Corny, I know.
But it was just a dream,
what can I say?
[MOM] It's not such
a bad dream.
[DAD] Oh?
[MOM] Well, it means we'd
be together forever, right?
[Dad chuckles]
[DAD] Silly girl.
[both laugh]
[SUN] Is that you, Father?
[SUN] Good morning,
hope you slept well.
Oh, yes, Sun,
I slept very well.
Thank you.
Good morning.
[MOM] What are you
standing there gawking at?
Oh, hi, honey,
so there you are.
Don't sound too
excited to see me.
Sorry... I was just
daydreaming a little bit...
...about being young.
[MOM] So you like
staring at young girls
and daydreaming, do you?
[DAD] That's not what I meant!
You've got it all wrong!
[MOM] Just what's
so great about youth?
[DAD] Uh--youth means
"never looking back."
[NAGASUMI] Good morning.
[MOM] Tell me,
what is love, Nagasumi?
[NAGASUMI] I think it's
"never hesitating"!
Oh, hey there,
Nagasumi. Good morning.
[NAGASUMI] Good morning, Sun.
[Nagasumi sighs]
[NAGASUMI THINKS] I never
knew that anyone
could look so good in an apron.
[SUN]
Hmm?
Oh, uh, don't mind me.
It's nothing, really!
It's true what they say:
like father, like son.
What're you saying?
Our Nagasumi isn't causing
you any trouble in school is he?
Nope. It's the
other way around.
I'm the one who's always
causin' Nagasumi trouble.
You sure that bringing
your future bride
with you to school
hasn't affected
your concentration
at least a little?
I hope not.
Actually we're
kinda keeping the
marriage stuff
a secret between us.
Secret? Why?
It was his choice.
I told him how
much I hate secrets.
Mom, let's just
say that life in
junior high school is more
complicated than you remember.
[GIRL 1] Wow, Sun,
your hair is so silky!
Hey, tell us
your secret.
What shampoo do you use?
Um, I guess it's,
it's salt water.
Oh, do you mean that deep
sea water cleansing stuff?
[GIRL 3] And you don't
have a single zit either!
[NAGASUMI THINKS]
It's awesome that Sun's getting
along so well with everyone.
Though I have to admit...
I'm not sure how happy
I am about having to
share her with other people,
but that's a little
ridiculous, I guess.
[SARU] Hey Nagasumi.
You should see
your face right now.
You're like a lovesick puppy.
[BOY 1] How did you get to be
so tight with Sun, huh?
Are you a ladies' man
now or something?
[BOY 2] I'm so jealous!
[SARU] Yeah, what's
with you, you fappy bastard?
What's wrong with you?
Why are you kissing me?
[MAWARI] Hey!
You hoodlums over there!
[MAWARI] You think you can
just mess around like that?
Maybe I should
teach you a little
lesson about the
rules of this school.
[NAGASUMI] Mawari!
[MAWARI] You gonna
be okay, Nagasumi?
Help me!
Sun, please help!
Mean Mawari is picking on me!
Jeez. What's wrong
with that girl anyway?
She always seems to show up
when Nagasumi's
involved in something.
Chimp, would ya
mind tellin' me some more
about what Nagasumi was
like when he was a little kid?
Um, he and Mawari
have been real
close friends for as long
as I can remember.
[SARU] You would never see
one of them without the other.
[SUN] Oh really?
Yep. Those two were
absolutely inseparable.
They even won a karuta
contest as team mates.
[MAWARI] Yeah!
The elementary karuta duels!
We won the first and second
grade division twice in a row!
When they talk about
the Karuta Queen of
Isono Elementary
School, they mean me!
Karuta queen?
[MAWARI] Hearing the word
'karuta' has got my blood going.
It's about time that
we had a match, Karuta King!
I don't know about you,
but I'm actually not all that
proud of my elementary
school nickname.
[VIDEO GAME VOICE] Three.
Two. Fight!
Be careful of dark alleys.
And beware of mistaken arrests.
[NAGASUMI] It's mine!
[CLASS REP] And now I'm
cursed to work for the cops.
[MAWARI] Mine!
[CLASS REP] No need to fear jail
cells if we all go in together.
[MAWARI] Mine!
[CLASS REP] Drop your weapon
now and turn yourself in.
[MAWARI] Mine, mine, mine!
This karuta game
is starting to
become a little
too scary for me.
Are you gonna
be alright, Sun?
[SUN] Uh, yeah.
I can't let a game
make me lose my nerve.
[NAGASUMI] You sure?
Your cheeks look a
little paler than usual.
Don't push
yourself too hard.
[CLASS REP] Aim to be
Superintendent General.
[SUN] Right!
Look Nagasumi!
I did it!
Congratulations!
[SUN] I couldn't've
done it without ya!
[NAGASUMI]
Really? Hey.
Uh, this card isn't
it your favorite, Mawari?
[MAWARI] Yeah...
...that one's always
been my favorite.
[SUN] Look, Nagasumi!
I did it.
[NAGASUMI] Congratulations!
What the heck has gotten
into you now, Mawari?
When did I start being
such a pouty girl?
[MAWARI] There's
something about watching
Nagasumi with Sun
that bothers me.
[MAWARI] It feels like a police
siren is going off in my heart.
[MAWARI] We have an
emergency on our hands!
This is a code red!
This is no way for me to behave!
Get your act together,
Mawari Zenigata!
[MAWARI] Starting tomorrow,
I'll double my efforts!
[MAWARI] You there!
No walking more than two
abreast on the sidewalk!
And you two over there!
No flirting on your
way to school!
You, young man!
No messing with your cell
phone while you're walking!
Hey you stop
that right now!
Maybe you all need to be taught
a lesson about the
rules of this society!
[NAGASUMI] See you later.
I'll take another
beer, please.
[NAGASUMI] Oh, Mawari!
[SUN] Officer Mawari, uh.
[MAWARI] You two over there!
Do you care to explain
to me why you're
coming out of the
same house together?
Whoa that's bright!
Turn it down.
That's right. And now
you're gonna talk.
Tell me why you and Sun came out
of the same house this morning.
Did you hear the
latest news, neighbor?
You'll never believe it!
Nagasumi and Sun
were seen coming
out of the same
house this morning.
Oh, well, I never!
I wonder what
their relationship is!
[NAGASUMI]
My husband can't find out.
Don't tell him.
I'm begging you!
This is awful!
Poor Nagasumi!
Officer Mawari's
taken him into custody!
So what's your answer?
You gonna squeal?
Ya see, Sun and
I have our reasons.
And they're good ones.
Reasons? Oh, now
this I'm interested in.
Please, tell me one good
reason a couple of junior high
school kids are sleeping
together under the same roof.
[NAGASUMI THINKS]
I don't know why,
but this little act of
hers is exciting me.
[MAWARI] Well, what
do you have to say.
Your 'reasons,'
can't wait to hear them.
[NAGASUMI THINKS]
I don't mind this too much.
Maybe I'll keep my
mouth shut a while longer.
[MAWARI] Here...
Fried pork with rice!
You'd better eat it while
it's still hot, don't you think?
[NAGASUMI THINKS] It looks so
good, but I have to be strong!
Oh, why do I feel such
a burning need to eat this?
--[SUN] Don't do it Nagasumi,
--My mouth is watering just from
--I'm warnin' ya!
--sitting here looking at it.
[MAWARI] So why don't
you take a little bite?
[NAGASUMI] Don't mind if I do.
[SUN] He's done it!
It's all over! Mawari wins!
[MAWARI] Just fess up, Nagasumi.
You'll feel much better.
Oh, the truth
is pretty simple.
Sun and I are
living together now.
[GOZABURO] Seriously?
The two of you
are living together?
What's the
meaning of this?
Please spare me,
Officer Mawari!
The two of
them are related.
That's why they live together.
Oh, so you're
related now, huh?
Where are your parents then?
What are they doing?
Um, Officer Mawari,
ya see, my dad is--
I'm right over here, darlin'.
Don't you worry about me haha.
[SUN] He's usin'
some old-fashioned
instruments of
torture on Nagasumi.
[GOZABURO] No way in
hell I'll ever let a filthy
maggot like you live with
my Sun, ya hear me?
You're gonna pay for this!
[NAGASUMI] No, please stop it!
Okay, I understand now.
Mister Seto is Sun's dad.
I did wonder about that,
given that their last
names are the same.
In that case,
what about your mother?
Where is she hiding, huh?
--Alright you puny piss-ant.
--[SUN] Um, my mother is.
[REN] Time for you to calm down.
[SUN] My mom's over there.
looking after my dad.
[BOY 1] They came to
school as a family?
[BOY 2] Can a parent be in
charge of his child's class?
[SUN] We got the
principal's permission for it.
[MAWARI] Sun, tell us exactly.
[CLASS] Who are you?
[MAWARI] Is the rest
of your family living
in Nagasumi's house with you?
[SUN] Naw, Mom and
Dad live somewhere
else 'cause of,
family circumstances.
[BOY 1] That complete loser...
[BOY 2] ...is actually
living with Sun?
[NAGASUMI] Sun, I'll save you!
[NAGASUMI THINKS]
Sun got hit full-on with water!
She'll change back
into mermaid form!
[NAGASUMI] Sun,
are you all right?
Here, let me dry
your legs for you.
It shouldn't take too long.
I'm really sorry
about that, Sun.
[BOY 1] Nagasumi, you dirty rat.
[BOY 2] How dare you
rub her legs like that!
What's going on?
I saw it a tail.
I don't know what the heck is
going on with these people!
[NAGASUMI THINKS] Mawari
was acting weird yesterday.
Could she have seen Sun's tail?
Mermaid law states that
if a human finds out
about one of the sea folk,
either the human or
the mermaid has to die.
But today Mawari's
just been studying
like normal, so maybe
there's no problem.
Yeah, of course. Anyone
would think it was just
their eyes playing
tricks on them.
Oh no, my hand slipped.
I spilled some water!
Nagasumi barrier!
Nagasumi!
His reaction!
He protected her.
Does that mean something weird
happens to her legs
when they get wet?
[NAGASUMI THINKS] She's onto us!
Mawari, I don't know
what you're talking about.
I saw that Sun was going to
get wet, so I shielded
her, that's all.
That isn't all!
I saw her legs turn into
a fish tail yesterday.
Drenching someone
because you had
some sort of delusion
is incredibly rude.
I know it sounds crazy,
but I'm telling
you that's what I saw!
[NAGASUMI THINKS]
I'm sorry, Mawari,
but this is for your own good.
Please, drop it!
[MAWARI]
Nagasumi, remember,
my family has been in law
enforcement for centuries.
[MAWARI] Right now,
my cop sense is telling me
Sun isn't what she seems to be,
so don't you dare to lie to me!
[NAGASUMI THINKS] Dammit!
Mawari's cop sense?
We're in real trouble!
[SUN] It's okay Nagasumi,
it's what I expected.
We can talk about
honor among thieves,
but in the end, we yakuza
are fugitives from the law.
Attractin' the attention of the
police is somethin'
that we're used to.
Great. 'Honor among
thieves' mode.
Too much about
that girl is unnatural.
From now on I'm gonna
watch her like a hawk.
Just like a good
police officer would!
[MAWARI] Oh, sorry Sun.
I didn't mean to turn
the water so high.
Nagasumi barrier!
[MAWARI] Nagasumi!
[MAWARI] Whoops!
I tripped! How clumsy of me!
[garbled]
Nagasumi barrier!
[MAWARI] Huh?
[MAWARI]
Oh! Sorry!
[MAWARI] Looks like
my hand slipped again!
[NAGASUMI garbled]
Nagasumi barrier!
[SUN] Nagasumi!
Get out! You're a boy!
You're not allowed in here!
[MAWARI] What the hell are you
doing in the girls' bathroom?
Bastard!
So he thinks he can
follow my daughter
into the girls' bathroom
to peep at her, does he?
[MASA] Boss, no
swords in the school!
Come on Boss! Boss, please
put the sword down!
[OCTOPUS] After schooly.
[MAWARI] Stare.
[MAKI] Hey, Miss Sun!
Miss Sun!
Oh, Maki, hey.
Someone's been
spying on you,
haven't they, Miss Sun?
Uh-huh.
Leave it me.
I'll take care of it.
I'll dispose of
that little creep.
Let me at 'em.
No, Maki.
Don't do that.
But...
Ya see, I'm not
even sure whether
she's found out
everything or not.
--[NAGASUMI] Help me!
--[GOZABURO] You maggot!
I'm gonna kill ya, maggot!
[MAKI] The boss is
still goin' at it, huh?
[SUN] Part of the
reason Nagasumi's
workin' so hard is
to protect Mawari.
As his wife,
I gotta do my best to
protect her, too,
dontcha see, Maki?
[MAKI] Miss Sun.
He isn't keepin' the
secret just to protect me.
If officer Mawari
finds out about me,
then mermaid law demands that
she get the death penalty.
[MAWARI THINKS] Sun's
hiding something all right.
She goes to such great
lengths to avoid water.
Almost impossible
to believe.
But that girl is,
she must be!
[MAWARI] Sun!
[SUN] Officer Mawari!
I know, you
can't hide from me.
You're a fish aren't you!
So close!
Don't say that!
Your innocent act's not
gonna work on Officer Mawari.
Take a look at this.
That, tha-that
looks like a--
[MAWARI] A cat.
I'm sure you
know cats love fish.
You can fool a human,
but do you really think
you can fool a cat?
[NAGASUMI] Mawari,
you kinda sound like a moron.
[MAWARI] What'd you say?
Not a cat!
[NAGASUMI] Yet,
your plan is working.
And that's not
the only one I've got.
Go!
[MAWARI] Take that!
Full-speed cat attack!
Miss Sun, a mermaid's
weapon is her voice!
Use your howling voice
to stop the cat attack!
No, Maki!
Mawari's watching!
[SUN] And Chimp is here too!
Nagasumi barrier!
[NAGASUMI] NO! The cats
are just going around me!
[MAWARI] Huh. The cats
actually are swarming her.
That could
only happen to
someone who's
as beautiful as Sun.
I'll take care of
the humans
if you deal with these cats.
Please, just use
your howling voice!
[SUN] No Maki. I don't
wanna mess up the life
I have right now, even
if that life includes Mawari!
I can't use my mermaid
powers right now,
even if cats are bitin' me.
[MAKI] Please, Miss Sun.
[NAGASUMI] Mawari.
Why are you doing this?
[NAGASUMI] Stop trying
to figure out everyone's
secrets just for your
own sick curiosity!
[NAGASUMI] What
has Sun ever done
to deserve this from you?
Has she caused
anyone any problems?
Look what a hard
time you're giving her!
The Mawari I know would
never do anything
like this to someone.
[MAWARI] No!
That's not fair!
That isn't fair!
[NAGASUMI] Mawari, wait!
[car honks and tires screech]
Look out, Mawari!
Ultrasonic Level Reached!
[SUN] Howling voice!
[MAWARI THINKS]
What's happening?
[NAGASUMI] Mawari, you're alive.
[MAKI] I don't understand.
Why did you save that human?
[SUN] Ya see, Maki.
I couldn't let Officer Mawari
die just because
I was concerned about
keepin' my own secret safe.
If I did, that would be a
disgrace to all Seto mermaids.
[SUN] Because honor among
thieves is honor under the seas.
Where am I?
In the hospital, Mawari.
[NAGASUMI]
You have a concussion.
But they say the driver
of the car wasn't hurt.
[NAGASUMI THINKS] Sun
used one of her mermaid
powers right in front of her.
[NAGASUMI] I guess I should
prepare for the worst.
[SARU] Hot Mawari!
Oh, I guess
you're awake already?
Oh, hi Chimp.
[SARU] Sun sure saved you
from an ugly situation, huh?
What's that?
Sun saved me?
[SARU] But holy crap,
Sun, you've really got a hell
of a loud voice if it was enough
to cause a car accident.
Did you say a
loud voice, Chimp?
[SARU] I've never heard such
an incredible voice before.
You could be on tv!
A loud voice? Seriously?
Chimp, that's the
understatement of the century.
Okay, Mawari, how would
you describe a voice like that?
I guess I would
say her voice was--
You're absolutely
right, Chimp.
Sun's sure got an
incredible gift, doesn't she?
Yeah, that's
our Sun for ya.
[MAWARI] You're gonna
write that off as a gift?
[nervous laughter]
You're really
going to say that a
voice that sends cars
flying is nothing but a gift.
Maybe you two need a lesson
about the rules of this society.
[NAGASUMI]
Hey Chimp, you're a good man.
[VOICES] This is a
vase of water spilling.
[VOICES] And the
person being spilled on.
Thank you, Sun. You really
saved me back there.
I'm sorry.
I shouldn't have
been so suspicious.
Officer Mawari.
Just call me Mawari.
Okay, Sun?
I suppose I'll let
the human live today.
But only outta
respect for Miss Sun.
I do apologize.
I really don't know
what got into me.
[NAGASUMI] Neither do I.
It really wasn't
like you at all.
Well duh, it's because
Mawari's totally in lo--
Arrest for perjury.
Thank you all again
for your assistance today.
From now on I'll
stick to doing my job.
I'll devote myself
strictly to my duty,
and someday I'll be
an even greater
Superintendent
General than my dad!
Salute!
[MAWARI] Come on!
Don't drag your heels!
What did Chimp start
to say just a second ago?
Dunno.
I couldn't really
hear what he said.
[MAWARI THINKS]
Thank you for this Nagasumi.
♪
[NAGASUMI] Okay,
this is a secret from Sun,
but I'm a huge fan of this
pop star named Lunar!
Look, sure I have a bride,
but this is a totally
different issue.
We can draw a
clear line there, right?
Wait, why is Lunar passed
out in front of my house?
She's Sun's childhood friend?
This is amazing!