[CHIMP] The sonar's picking
up depth charges ahead!
I don't get it;
why are you even here?
Wherever my
lord goes, I follow.
When he told
me he needed
my help on this
simulated battle reality show
he's competing on, there was no
way I could turn him down!
[NAGASUMI] Huh?
Yeah, you know,
the reality TV show!
That's why we're
here, too, right?
So, was this
your idea?
My lord's gonna beat
the other team on live TV!
I sure am,
and when I win,
I'm gonna give the entire
million-yen prize to ya, Chimp!
Are you for real?
[KAI] Yep, so fight hard!
[CHIMP] As you wish, my lord!
[NAGASUMI] They're fooling you!
This isn't a TV show!
♪
[CREW A] Impact!
[CREW B] We're hit!
[CREW C] We'll have
to go around them!
We don't have time!
Bust straight through them!
Forward!
Why are there depth
charges down here?
Because Yoshiuo
wants to keep his special
little party pad away
from prying eyes!
Wait, "Yoshiuo,"
who's that?
[LUNAR] A perverted lady-killing
creep of a nobleman!
And the guy who kidnapped Sun!
Dammit...
Can't this crate
go any faster, Kai?
I swear, if he's laid a hand
on Sun, so help me, I'll--
Why you?
We're gonna give you
an earful for that, Yoshiuo!
Oh no, she
doesn't mean--?
I'm the songstress
of the Edomae!
[LUNAR] (screeching voice)
Don't underestimate me!
Honey, I'm home!
Huh? Hey, where's Nagasumi?
[MOM] Beats me...
He might not come
home for a while.
[MOM] He is a boy, you know.
Yeah you're right.
[Lunar laughs wickedly]
Is that all you've got?
Bring it on!
Alright then...
I'm bouncin'.
Hang on.
[GOZABURO] Chaser!
How'd ya like
that, rock?
You're not so to--
[GOZABURO]
What the hell is this?
[GOZABURO] I gotta save Sun!
To think even the boss
couldn't smash through it.
Diamond hard?
Sure seems
so, and I'd bet all
the other walls are
just as tough, too.
[SHARK] So this
time we're really
in big trouble, I guess?
[MAKI] Ya got that right!
"Nobility," my ass!
That freakin' perverted gigolo!
If he lays so much
as one finger on
Miss Sun, I'll kill
'em three times over!
[MASA] Maki, stop!
[SHARK] You might hit us?
Calm down, Maki.
[MAKI] Yes ma'am.
Ya mean well,
but kickin' up
a ruckus like that won't help.
[MAKI] But if something
happens to Miss Sun I'll...
[MAKI] I'll...
Maki...
We gotta do somethin'!
That's creep's got Sun!
[REN] It's all my
fault that he does.
If only I hadn't
brought Sun along,
this never would have happened.
Our daughter would be safe.
[MASA] Ma'am...
[MAKI] No, please
don't blame yourself.
[metal impact]
[GOZABURO THINKS]
Think Gozaburo,..
Do somethin' to get outta here,
get your little
girl back, and then
massacre the slimy
little turd who took her!
[chit chat and laughs]
[GROUPIE A] Whoa,
this is the girl?
[GROUPIE B] You're right!
This Sun's a major hottie!
She is pretty cute.
Oh, yeah? Well who's
cuter, me or her?
So didja, use that
special incense on
her that you use
on all your chicks?
Yeah...
[YOSHIUO] I pumped
her full of it, dude!
She's so scorching hot I
think I might even marry her!
Whoa, man...
It's that serious?
Well...
I always thought Sun from the
Seto gang was a total babe,
so I had her brought here.
But she's been here
'least an hour now,
and I haven't done anything yet.
[YOSHIUO] If that's not "love,"
I don't know what is.
What about me?
[YOSHIUO] Huh?
And me, too, Yoshiuo?
I thought I was
your number one girl?
I'm like a noble,
so even if I get married,
I can have as many
babes as I want.
[CHICKS] Awww...
[guys laugh]
[GROUPIE B] Now that's what I
call an open marriage, dude!
When it comes to chicks,
variety's key, right?
Isn't he awesome?
[GROUPIE C]
Isn't Sun a mob girl?
You sure you
wanna mess with her?
[YOSHIUO] Get real, dude!
Those mob punks
would never defy a noble!
'Specially not the
most powerful one of all!
[all laugh]
[YOSHIUO] Akeno,
baby, come over here!
Why are you being
such a wet blanket?
Sorry Lord Yoshiuo...
If you keep stepping
over the line like this,
I won't know what to report
to headquarters in Kyoto.
Oh?
Well, forget Kyoto
and those old farts there.
Even if they found out,
they wouldn't dare
make a move on me;
I scare the crap out of 'em.
I bet they wear adult
diapers 'cause of you!
[AKENO] Regardless...
[YOSHIUO]
Get this straight, baby:
I make the rules in
this place, not Kyoto!
[YOSHIUO]
And, like, another thing:
Doesn't your family
tradition say you can't
ever go against a
noble no matter what?
Well, isn't that true,
Miss Training Swordsman?
Yeah, I thought so.
Now that we've got
that straightened out,
like, go find Sun
and help her get ready
'cause like,
right after this party,
I'm gonna get married!
[GROUPIE B] He's serious!
[CHICK B] Seriously hilarious!
[GROUPIE C] You da man!
[AKENO] This is insane!
[AKENO] What am I doing?
[NAGASUMI] Sun!
I'm coming!
[MECHANICAL VOICE] We're
about to charge the enemy.
Please watch your step.
All crew,
brace for impact!
[KAI] Charge!
[MAKI] What the hell?
[SHARK] An air raid?
[REN] Could it be--?
Boss,
do you think it's--?
The maggot.
[GROUPIE A] What was that?
[GROUPIE B] Maybe it was,
like, an earthquake?
Where's security? Just sitting
on their butts again?
[GUARD A] Is that an alarm?
[GUARD B] I dunno.
[LUNAR] Ow!
Hey, charge a little more
smoothly next time, would ya?
[CHIMP] Whoa,
what a flashy place!
Yoshiuo!
Sun, I'm here!
[SOLDIER A] Who are you?
[NAGASUMI] Someone who didn't
know he'd be facing an army!
And not just any army,
but Yoshiuo Minamoto's!
You fools don't stand
a chance against us!
[CHIMP] Au contraire!
[NAGASUMI] Wait... Chimp?
Your puny little army
doesn't stand a chance,
because you're
going up against the next
head of the Mikawa Conglomerate,
the great and
powerful Kai Mikawa!
[NAGASUMI] Oh, man!
You tell 'em, Chimp!
Now open a path for me!
[NAGASUMI] You can't
take 'em alone, moron!
[CREW A] Follow the
young master's lead, men!
[CREW B] Make the
Mikawa Conglomerate proud!
[SOLIDER A]
For the house of Minamoto!
[KAI] Move it!
Wow... Look at
all these people!
Talk about your
cast of thousands!
[LUNAR] Out of our way, Chimp!
We'll back you all up
How, Lunar?
Open your minds!
The Ancient Mermaid Lyrics
for the Song of War!
[LUNAR] Take Two!
No, you idiot,
if you do that--
[LUNAR] ♪ ... with me, waken
from your sleep, rise up. ♪
♪ Let your rage reign free, ♪
♪ let your hatred
be your guide now. ♪
[NAGASUMI] Oh, not good.
They've degenerated.
[NAGASUMI] Into something
unbroadcastable!
[SOLDIER A] Die! All of you!
Wait a sec,
how come I'm okay?
[NAGSUMI'S FEMALE XO]
Ability activated!
[LUNAR] Hey, Nagasumi!
[LUNAR] Yoshiuo's more
than likely in the great hall!
[LUNAR] So get going,
manservant!
[NAGASUMI] Right!
[LUNAR] We'll take
care of things here!
Aw bummer, the
champagne spilled.
So, like, what was
that tremor anyway?
Dunno, but it
killed the mood.
[YOSHIUO]
You guys aren't making it
any better with your moaning.
[YOSHIUO] You're, like,
totally bumming me out.
[GROUPIE B] Dude.
[YOSHIUO] I need
to get cheered back up,
so I'm gonna go
get married to Sun.
[GROUPIE B] Seriously?
[YOSHIUO] Yeah!
I'll, like, catch you guys
after the marriage has
been consummated.
[NAGASUMI] Yoshiuo!
[YOSHIUO] Huh?
I know you're
in here somewhere!
You might be a noble and all,
but I won't let you have Sun!
[YOSHIUO] Oh?
Who's that dude?
Hey, wait,
don't tell me.
You're that little
junior high kid who's,
claiming to be Sun's husband
or something, aren't you?
Yeah, that's me!
[NOBLEMAN A] A human?
[NOBLEWOMAN A] How weird.
Well, I'm
Yoshiuo, bro.
So if you've got something
to say then make it snappy.
So you're Yoshiuo?
Give me back Sun!
[YOSHIUO] Hang on.
Did you chase her here
all the way from Saitama?
Gross-out me out, dude!
You're a total stalker!
[NAGASUMI] You're the gross-out,
now give her back!
This dude's sporting
a serious 'tude.
I can't deal with him.
So sweep this trash
away for me, Akeno baby.
Akeno?
The heck are you doing
in Yoshiuo's palace?
[NAGASUMI] Akeno?
[AKENO] I am a
training swordsman,
so I can't disobey
a noble's direct order.
[YOSHIUO] Been nice
knowing you, dude.
Don't worry, I'll take real
good care of Sun for you.
I plan on having a
whole lotta fun with her,
even if she is your leftovers.
[NAGASUMI] Huh? "Leftovers?"
[YOSHIUO] Wait! What!
You mean, like you
never touched her?
That's so awesome!
Why didn't you tell me sooner?
Keep your
hands off of her!
[NAGASUMI] Akeno, please.
[AKENO] I'm sorry, Nagasumi.
You're not in junior
high anymore, dude.
This is the adult world.
[YOSHIUO] People
totally get hurt and die,
as you're about to find out
thanks to Akeno baby there.
Akeno!
We can't let a guy
like that have Sun!
[AKENO] It's time to face facts:
a mermaid-human marriage
was impossible to begin with.
What the hell are
you talking about?
[AKENO] I'm sorry.
I can't stop this.
[YOSHIUO]
Quit being such a drag!
Hurry up and fillet
that dude, would ya?
[AKENO] Give up on
Sun Seto and beg forgiveness!
If you do it right now,
Lord Yoshiuo
will spare your life!
Yep, I will, I'm
a big-hearted dude.
[NAGASUMI] No.
[YOSHIUO] Huh?
[NAGASUMI]
No way will I give up!
Are you crazy?
Give up!
No, never!
For your sake, do it!
You're the one who's
being crazy, Akeno!
You didn't master the sword
so you could do stuff like this!
[NAGASUMI] I know you didn't!
[YOSHIUO] Waste him.
What the--?
[AKENO] You're right.
[AKENO] I can't use my sword
for something I know is wrong.
So, Nagasumi... I'll
fight by your side now!
[NAGASUMI] Wait you will?
[AKENO] There is no waver in the
glow of the
Morning Star tonight!
The sword of heaven, huh?
Don't get carried away, babe.
[CAPTAIN SWORDSMAN]
Writing the report about
this is going to be interesting.
But that Akeno,
she's just like her brother.
[AKENO] Nagasumi,
no matter what happens,
just promise me you'll
get Sun out of here!
Right! That's why
I came here!
You have my word!
I'll never let that
scumbag have Sun!
Not ever!
Hah! You two
are pissing me off.
Why don't you,
like, drop dead, okay.
[NAGASUMI] What's going on?
[NAGASUMI AND AKENO]
It... It's a--!
[NAGASUMI] A giant eel?
[AKENO] Move!
[NAGASUMI] Akeno!
[YOSHIUO]
Say hello to my pet, dude.
He's, like, all
omnivorous and stuff.
[YOSHIUO] Meaning,
like, he'll eat anything:
humans, mermaids, whatever!
And he's always hungry, dude!
Nagasumi!
[GOZABURO]
"Never," huh?
[GOZABURO] That wasn't a
bad shout ya gave back there...
Dad, you're here!
Don't call me "Dad,"
ya piss ant!
[GOZABURO] Hey, Yoshiuo!
[GOZABURO]
You're gonna pay for screwin'
with the Seto's, ya damn punk!
Like I have time
for that, old dude.
Hey um, I need you guys here,
like, right way, okay!
[ELITE GUARD A] Chill out.
Keep your shirt on,
bro, we're here.
[ELITE GUARD B]
You sounded like you
were about to freak, man.
What's the dealio?
[GOZABURO] Who the
hell are these punks?
[YOSHIUO] Thanks!
I'll leave these
two dudes to you!
Hey! Hold it!
[ELITE GUARD]
Roger that, Yoshiuo!
We'll, like, totally chop these
lame-o's up
into itty-bitty pieces!
[MAKI] Not if my
Liquid Machine Gun
has anything to say about it!
[NAGASUMI] What the--?
[NAGASUMI] Maki!
[MAKI] That wasn't too
shabby for a sea louse!
[MASA] Nagasumi...
I heard that speech you made.
Nice job, I'm proud of you.
[SHARK]
Sorry, guys, but the only
one who can eat Nagasumi...
...is me.
Masa!
Shark Fujishiro!
I just knew ya
had somethin'
to do with that tremor!
So you're here, too?
Mom, are all of you guys okay?
[GOZABURO] We're fine,
and we're gonna be a whole
lot better once we teach
these nobles a lesson!
Let's show 'em what happens
when you mess with the Setos!
[MASA AND SHARK AND MAKI]
Sure, Boss, whatever you say!
Where did it get ya?
The legs,
but they're not that bad.
[SHARK] Time to eat?
[ELITE GUARD D] No! Don't! Stop!
[REN] If he keeps
eatin' that fast,
he's gonna get a
bad stomach ache.
[REN] Hey, Nagasumi.
We'll handle the rest.
This place isn't safe,
so get out of here.
[NAGASUMI] No.
[NAGASUMI] I can't!
I'm not leaving until
I've saved Sun!
[NAGASUMI] I will not and
cannot let her down!
I wouldn't be here
today if it wasn't for Sun.
I was drowning,
and she saved me.
Even though she knew she'd die
if she did it,
she still saved me.
A total stranger.
That was so selfless of her.
[NAGASUMI]
I learned something really
important from Sun that day.
There's some
things in this world
more important than my own life!
That's the Seto gang's
honor among thieves!
[Gozaburo grunts]
[NAGASUMI]
A good husband's supposed to
protect his wife
and keep her safe!
I will do that!
Sun's real lucky to have
a guy like you, Nagasumi.
Hey! Don't you
forget what ya said!
[GOZABURO] 'Cause you're
a Seto, now maggot!
[GOZABURO] Now go.
Right!
[ELITE GUARD E]
As if we'd let you go, dude!
[ELITE GUARD F]
You're going down, bro!
No, you are!
Thanks, Lunar!
Manservant!
[CHIMP] Ow, my freakin ears.
That was so loud.
What are ya...
waitin' for?
[SHARK] Nagasumi?
[MAKI] Grow some balls
and get Sun back!
You can do it, Nagasumi!
We're countin' on ya!
Go! Get your bride
back, Nagasumi!
[Nagasumi cries out]
What the hell?
There's two of 'em now?
Miss Ren!
Can you sing at the same pitch?
As the sword, sure.
[REN] But my voice...
[REN] (distorted)
It ain't as pretty!
And now's my chance!
What the hell?
You mean there are
three of them now?
[LUNA PAPA] I told
you I'd be back!
Edomae?
You're in
that outfit again?
It's no problemo!
Papa! Terminate 'em!
[LUNAR PAPA] Lunar!
Oh, man!
This is just like being
in a big-budget blockbuster!
[LUNAR] Eat beam!
[Lunar laughs wickedly]
[YOSHIUO] Man,
what's the deal with, like,
everyone getting in
my freaking way today?
Nothing pisses me
off more than people
getting between me
and having a good time.
[YOSHIUO] Like
we're about to have.
[Yoshiuo snickers]
[NAGASUMI] Sun!
[YOSHIUO] Huh?
[YOSHIUO] What's your damage?
You're, like, seriously
stubborn, you know that?
You shut up!
Don't worry Sun!
I'll get you out of
this place right now!
[YOSHIUO] And, like, totally
mess up my wedding night?
No way, dude!
[YOSHIUO] Did you
really think a human
could take on mermaid nobility?
Man, you're a dumbass!
Sun...
[NAGASUMI] Come on Sun.
Why aren't ya--
Saying anything?
I gave her a little somethin'
to keep her quiet.
It also keeps
her from hearing you.
[NAGASUMI] What is this stuff?
[YOSHIUO]
You could, like, call it a
secret mermaid treasure.
Humans can't
stand the smell of it,
but it doesn't have
any effect on 'em;
just mermaids.
So that's why
Sun's so out of it!
You gassed her with that stuff!
Duh, dude,
it'd be a real drag
if she started fighting back!
You lousy, no-good son of a--!
[YOSHIUO] Dude,
haven't you learned?
You can't beat a mermaid noble.
I'm, like, way stronger.
Don't care.
It doesn't matter
how strong you are,
I'll never let you have Sun!
That's freaking hilarious!
I bet Sun would laugh, too,
if she could hear you right now!
Sun, please listen.
[NAGASUMI] I don't know
if you can hear me,
but I came to get you.
Sorry I'm so late.
And speaking of sorry,
I want to apologize
for that fight we had.
It was all my fault;
I took you for granted.
[NAGASUMI] I'm sorry...
I'll turn my socks
inside-out from now on.
I won't leave tissues
in my jeans, either.
I'll even rinse my plates off,
whatever it takes.
[NAGASUMI] Because I...
[NAGASUMI] Because I love you,
and I can't imagine
living without you!
[YOSHIUO] Dude, you're,
like, being a serious drag!
Stay by my side!
We can't let things
end like this!
Sun, please!
[YOSHIUO] I totally
can't stand drags.
[YOSHIUO] So it's time
for you to drop dead.
[SUN] Nagasumi...
Sun, you're awake!
What the--?
There's no freaking way!
[SUN] Nagasumi,
it's because of you...
I heard ya callin'.
Everythin' was
blank for so long.
And I couldn't hear
anythin' at all, but then...
But then I heard
your voice callin'
out my name from the darkness.
I knew you
could hear me.
I heard it when you said
that you loved me, Nagasumi.
That came from
your heart, didn't it?
Like way to spoil the surprise
I had planned for you.
[SUN] Yer a disgustin'
worm, Yoshiuo!
[SUN] What, ya hafta
resort to nasty
tricks like this just
to get a woman?
That would disgrace
all Seto mermaids!
You're nothin' more
than third-rate scum!
Third-rate?
If I knew you were gonna
be this much of a drag, Sun,
I never would have taken you!
You can just drop dead, too!
Fine by me if
you wanna die first!
Hey, you...
Yeah, what?
How dare you point
that thing at a girl?
How dare you point that
thing at Sun, you scumbag?
Nagasumi...
I'll sing the Song
of the Hero and--
[Sun gasps]
[SUN] Nagasumi!
Why so shocked?
I said I was gonna kill him!
[NAGASUMI] Now you've done it.
You've made me angrier
than I've ever been before!
[NAGASUMI] I, Nagasumi
Michishio, am more pissed off
than I've ever been
in my entire life!
Who...
or what is this guy?
Ya mean you're doin'
it without the Song of the Hero?
[NAGASUMI]
I don't need it anymore.
Just having you by my
side fills me with power.
[NAGASUMI]
As long as I'm with you, Sun.
I can be infinitely powerful!
[giant eels cry out]
Something's
scaring the eels, Papa!
Look, a storm
has come, my lord.
Yes! A Storm of Destiny!
No, this can't
be happening, dude!
Dude this is crazy!
[NAGASUMI] Listen up, Yoshiuo.
[NAGASUMI] There's
only one path that a
true man follows:
honor among thieves!
[SUN] There's only one thing
that a true man heeds.
Honor among thieves!
[SUN AND NAGASUMI] Because
"honor among thieves!"
is "honor under the seas."
But you can't beat me!
I'm a noble!
There's nothing
"noble" about you!
You disgrace our
honor among thieves!
[YOSHIUO] Ah!
What are you being
so serious for?
[NAGASUMI] 'Cause I'm deadly
serious about stopping you!
Ya know that honor
we were talkin' about?
You're about to get
a big taste of it!
Crushing blow!
That was for Sun,
and so is this one!
[YOSHIUO] My...
This one's for
Sun, too, Yoshiuo!
[YOSHIUO] Bride is!
And this one, it's
for Sun as well!
[YOSHIUONAGASUMI] A!
Put them all together,
and every single
one them is for Sun!
[NAGASUMI] Judgment!
[YOSHIUO] Mermaid!
So Yoshiuo's mermaid
form is a catfish?
Catfish, where?
I'm hungry!
[KAI] My eyes! My eyes! Arghh!
[ELITE GUARD G] Whoah!
Un-freaking-believable!
[ELITE GUARD H]
You're a catfish?
That's hilarious!
Say cheese, bro!
[YOSHIUO] No, stop it
[ELITE GUARD I]
You've gone straight from
cool to uncool, dude!
[CAPTAIN SWORDSMAN]
Lord Yoshiuo...
I have no choice now but to
inform Kyoto
of your actions here.
[CAPTAIN SWORDSMAN] Your
mischief went too far this time.
[SUN] Nagasumi...
[NAGASUMI] Sun.
[NAGASUMI] Um, well I, uh...
[Sun weeps]
I'm so sorry!
The fight was my fault!
[NAGASUMI] Not, it was
mine, and I'm sorry.
Please don't cry...
It won't happen again.
See because...
I need...
I need to ask you
something important.
[NAGASUMI] I love you.
Will you please
stay with me forever?
Of course!
I know I'm not
anything special but...
I'll always do my best to
make you happy, Nagasumi.
[yelling and pleading]
[MOM] Nagasumi!
Hurry up, your breakfast
is getting cold!
[NAGASUMI] (deep voice) Sun, why
did you let me oversleep?
[SUN] I tried real hard to
wake ya up several times,
but ya were sleepin' like a log!
[LUNAR] Well, obviously,
you didn't try hard enough!
Hey, you be
nice, Lunar.
Nagasumi, is it
just me, or is there
something different
about you today?
Hey, Sun, hurry up or
we're gonna be late for school!
[NAGASUMI] Then let's go.
[CHIMP] Something's different.
Is that some kind of myalgia
you've got there, Nagasumi?
[fake whistle sound]
[MAWARI] You're late again,
Mr. Habitually Tardy!
And you Sun Seto!
Where have you
been the last few days?
I don't care!
Late is late!
Maybe I should teach
you the rules of this society!
[SUN] Please let us off,
Officer Mawari, Ma'am!
Sun...
We could have somethin'
special together.
Just dump that
loser you're with.
Hey, Nagasumi, go and buy me a--
[KAI] Scratch that!
My, how vexing.
No one ever seems to
change around
this place, do they?
Well, aside from Nagasumi
getting all buff, that is.
[MAWARI] Do you hear me
Nagasumi Michishio?
♪
[VOICES] The end!