Remember...
Honor the covenant...
Do not forsake us.
Saya.
Oh, good morning, Father!
How're you?
It's still early...
What are you doing up?
You should've stayed
in bed and rested.
Don't worry;
I'm tough, remember?
Not just physically...
Your emotional wounds
need care as well.
Yes... I feel bad
about the baker...
I just couldn't
save him... and...
And?
Before the Elder Bairn died,
it told me something odd...
It said... for me to
honor the covenant.
They've never
spoken to me before.
Not until now.
I'm confused...
What it said...
This covenant...
Do you know what
it meant, Father?
What are these
Elder Bairns to you, Saya?
They are my enemies.
You must not allow yourself to
be distracted by their words...
Trust your heart... always.
Yes... I will.
♪ It's so nice
outside again today. ♪
♪ The same as it ever was. ♪
♪ Nothing really
changes much... ♪
♪ The cicadas
are singing too. ♪
♪ The clouds are white,
and the sky is blue ♪
♪ and I am feeling
wonderful. ♪
♪ I'm feeling wonderful! ♪
♪ It's so nice
outside again today. ♪
♪ The day once more
is full of peace. ♪
♪ The same as it ever was. ♪
♪ The gentle people
here have happy hearts ♪
♪ and peaceful souls. ♪
Father looked
so worried earlier.
It's because
I got hurt; I know it.
I need to be stronger for him.
I can't believe how, like, way
perfect the weather is again.
At least there's something
nice about today...
I heard some bad news earlier.
Oh... About the baker?
The bakery is still closed...
That's not good.
Looks like he never
did come back...
He's just gone.
A katana...? But why...
It's so strange.
I checked the
bakery this morning.
Some guy there told
me he was still missing...
So sad.
That police officer
went all the way
to Guimauve just to warn us.
They must have been
looking for him then.
Apparently nobody's
even heard from him.
I bet I know what happened.
He was probably over living
in this boring, crappy town
and just ran away from home.
I don't think it's
technically running away
if you're already an adult.
Then... what is it?
Uh, disappearing?
Yeah!
Hey!
And she's off!
It's the dog!
What dog?
Please, wait!
Watch out!
Please, get off, of me.
Oh! Um... I'm sorry...!
Are you hurt?
Uh... Do you need help?
The nurse?
Get off, first.
I'm so sorry, Tokizane!
At least you're not hurt, so...
Tell me... What were you
climbing that tree for anyway?
To catch the, dog.
A what?
A puppy...!
I mean... I'm not sure
if it's a real puppy...
...but it is really tiny.
And uh, how exactly did you end
up in a tree chasing this dog?
He was jumping from branch
to branch, so I followed him.
Sure it was a dog, not a... cat?
I'm sure! It was a dog.
Okay... Now, if you don't hurry
up and eat, lunch will be over.
Oh, yeah!
Well, aren't you gonna eat?
No, I prefer sleeping to eating.
That's not good...!
You have to eat;
otherwise, you'll get sad.
Uhhh... Haven't you
said that before?
Yes, I have, because it's true.
Of course... You're funny, Saya.
That looks nice!
What?
You look better
when you smile...
Did you know that?
Thank you.
We can share this
if you want to...
You'll like it; I promise...
Fumito's lunches are the best.
I'm sure you know him...
He owns Café Guimauve
next to the shrine...
Have you been there before?
I've been there.
Would you like a rice ball?
Does it taste okay?
It's good... I guess... Yeah.
Thanks! I'm glad you like it!
But you didn't make this, right?
Right...
It just makes me
happy when someone
compliments Fumito's cooking,
so I like to say thank you.
Okay, so what do you
think about this Fumito guy.
I love him.
Where do you think Saya went?
There is no telling.
Is something, wrong?
Why, exactly?
What?
Why do you love him?
I don't know;
I just really like him...
To start with, he's nice,
and he's the best
cook I've ever met,
and no matter what he's doing,
he always takes the
time to listen to me.
No, that's not what I mean!
So, that's all it
takes to love, then...?
He's a nice, cook
who listens to you?
Is that love...?
It seems too easy.
He really said that to you?
He did...
I'm not even sure
what his point was;
maybe I said
something to upset him.
No, I seriously doubt it.
Yeah?
He always seems like
he's upset with me, though.
I'm sure he's just got
his own stuff going on...
Don't forget he's still young.
It's yummy.
Your coffee is the best...
It never fails to
make me feel better.
Well, I do make it
just for you. Here.
Guimauve!
Yes, enjoy...
I think you've earned
something nice.
Thank you, Fumito!
Are you okay?
Hey... What's wrong?
Sorry... I just kind of
spaced out, I guess.
You sure you're okay?
I'm fine.
You know you can
talk to me, right?
No matter what it is.
I'm here.
Thanks.
It's not a simple thing to
change a person's emotions...
And, as long as those
feelings remain engraved
into their heart, it doesn't
really matter what they are.
I imagine the most
difficult emotion
to affect would be hatred...
Many people will tell you
such negativity doesn't last...
But that's not quite the
same as going away, is it...?
Hatred remains...
It only hides where
you cannot see it.
Given the slightest opportunity,
it will reassert itself.
Now then...
Given hatred's persistence...
What is one to do if they wish
to eliminate it for good...?
The only possibility
is to overthrow hatred
with an equally
powerful emotion.
I will protect them...
I promise.
To conquer an
emotion as strong as hatred...
Well... Only love
and trust will do.
Yamada!
What?
Get out of here, now!
Right!
Come on, let's go!
This isn't what they
said it would be.
I know.
I didn't realize they ate
their own kind, too.
Run...! Hurry!
Is it you...?
Are you the one who
is trying to destroy us?
It appears you do
not know how to fight.
The others...
He's controlling them.
You are the same.
The ones above
control those below.
Meanwhile, they work
for others above them.
But there are some things
that cannot be controlled.
Honor the covenant.
I don't... What covenant?
The Shrovetide.
The Shrovetide?
We eat because we must.
Let this be a warning.
Interfere again, and we
will dine on you as well.
You are my enemy.
All I do is fight.
Shrovetide...? I...
I can't...
This is...
Saya!
I did it.
Are you hurt?
Yes... But don't worry;
I should be all right...
There were three this time.
I killed them all.
And what were these
Elder Bairns like?
They said they
were the same as us.
They did?
They said... to honor
the covenant... again.
Nene Motoe?
Here!
Nono Motoe?
I'm so sorry I'm late!
Good morning, Saya...
I passed Kisaragi
in the K's, though.
I'm sorry; it won't
happen again.
Well, I haven't finished yet,
so I can give you
a break this time.
I completely understand
why you're late.
It's so gorgeous outside.
If you ask me, it's going
to be a perfect, peaceful day.
It's raining today.
I guess it had to eventually.
We won't have gym class,
so you can have a
study period, instead.
Let's tell ghost stories!
Talk about the best idea ever!
Yeah, um...
I don't think that's what a
study period is for, you guys.
What's wrong, Itsuki?
Are you worried you're
gonna get too scared?
No, that's not it at all!
Whatever. I'm going home.
Excuse me...
What exactly do you think
you're doing, Tokizane?
Next time on Blood-C:
"Meeting in the Way."