It's like no matter
what we do to try
and make her remember,
she just keeps changing back
into this lame
version of herself.
Seriously!
Every time we start thinking she
might know what's going on...
Whatever she remembers
goes like, right out the window.
I... What?
Didn't I tell you it's time
to stop all this nonsense?
You don't have to
keep playing the game.
We've spent the entire
summer on a farce,
and I'm done with it...
How long is long
enough for you, Saya?
The... summer?
What an idiot?!
She still doesn't get it!
We've been putting on this
stupid show for, like, ever...
You want some more proof?
This weird outfit isn't
even a real school uniform.
Ooh, nice!
At least we surprised
her a bit this time!
Do you know what one is
supposed to look like, though?
What uniform did you
wear in elementary school?
Or middle school...?
Do you know?
Do you remember who you
were in class with last year?
You don't, do you?
Would you like to know why?
It's because they
never existed, Saya.
Although, they might be planning
to introduce them
into the story later!
If it doesn't blow up
in their faces first.
But...
I, uh...
I know, you're on
your mother's path...
She was a shrine maiden, too.
What was her name again?
Do you happen to
have a picture of her?
Any specific childhood memories
of you and your beloved Father?
No. You don't have a
single memory, do you?
But I... I am...
Go on... Who are you?
I'm Saya... Kisaragi...
Kisaragi... Right.
Stupid.
Yeah, for real...
Giving her that name is
the most ridiculous
thing I've ever heard.
Hey...!
Do you know what
it means...? Kisaragi?
I don't.
Its meaning is to
change one's robes...
To become someone else...
For a girl who
has been convinced
she's someone she's not,
it may be the perfect name.
So... Miss Kisaragi...
No, Saya...
Even if your head is telling
you you're someone else...
I'm still willing to bet...
What's in here
hasn't changed at all.
I mean, not that we really
care or anything, though.
Sorry.
We just want to get back to
our own lives already, so...
Yeah.
We're not the only ones.
Tokizane?
How?
All I want to do
is finish this job
and get the money they owe me.
You are so totally heartless.
Like you two are any different.
The only reason
we're doing this is
so we can get other
jobs when we're done.
Can you blame us?
The economy is awful!
Are you telling me you
actually took main cast roles
in this stupid production out
of future employment concerns?
What does main cast roles mean?
Oh! It means we're very
important to the story!
It's the two of us, of course...
Your handsome Tokizane...
Yuka... Mister
Class Rep, Itsuki...
And, don't forget...
Kanako Tsutsutori.
All the other people
are cast as extras...
But... Just because we've
managed to stay alive...
...don't assume anyone
else had that luxury.
It's true...
The members of the main
cast are considered special...
So they gave us talismans
to keep those monsters away.
Pretty fancy protection, huh?
Then, all the people
who disappeared...
They're all...
They're all dead.
It's funny.
I've actually had a
really good time...
But...
I'm kinda over it now.
I know; it's just too
much work and time...
Especially for
such a boring reward.
What did they promise
to give you guys, anyway?
Funny story...
We were a little... bad...
And if the cops found out...
It could cause some trouble.
By trouble, she means
we'd probably go to jail.
Luckily... they said...
they'd take care of it.
And we won't have to worry
about it anymore... Yay!
So basically you're
both criminals?
Oh, get off your high horse.
Yeah, you knew the
extras were going to die,
and you didn't do
anything to help them.
Someone was having
too much fun playing
the "bad boy" role
and getting close
and personal with
the leading lady.
The hell I was.
Okay, okay.
That's enough...
Seriously, calm down.
You're freaking Saya out.
You're freaking her out more
than anyone else, Teacher!
Wait...
She's not a teacher at all!
Tell me that you brought it.
Yeah.
Hey!
Rude!
Is that what I think it is?
Yeah.
Nice...!
You talked about it,
but I didn't think you'd really
be able to come through!.
How'd you do it?
I pretended to be attacked
and got it when I ran.
What?! Crazy!!
I couldn't have done that...
It's insane!
I didn't want to
either... however...
I don't want to have to deal
with those nut jobs anymore
or with this monster.
Well...
As soon as we can
get Saya to drink,
things should start
moving along quickly.
That being said, I cannot
guarantee the results...
Do you understand?
Naturally.
Yeah.
All you have to do is
drink this... Trust me.
It's the blood of those
you call Elder Bairns.
Look how strong you are.
It would appear the
rumors are correct...
I see why the US military
and Japanese government
would want to keep you a secret.
Saya, an inhuman
thing in human form.
Does your strength come from
the fact that you aren't human?
Or is it because of the
life you've lived so far...?
I want to know.
I want you, Saya...
and for that to happen.
I need you to take a nap.
This is the effect of
drinking their blood...
She starts remembering.
Oh...
I've seen that before.
It's so weird, drinking
that nasty monster blood
makes her eyes turn
all red and creepy.
Haven't you seen
her do that, yet...?
I have... It was
when I pretended
to be attacked but
ran away instead.
After she killed
the monster thing,
she started drinking its blood.
Like on purpose drinking it.
Hey...
At least she's pretty!
You know, most inhuman
things found in legend
and myth are said
to be beautiful.
Really...? What happened
with those monsters, then?
The Elder Bairns
are hardly relevant...
Saya is special...
Originally, my research focused
on ancient poems and songs...
Did you know most
of those old verses
are packed with hidden riddles?
They aren't just
silly romantic balladry.
There are hidden stories
in almost all of them...
...bizarre creatures
and strange events...
Saya... That was where
I first heard about you...
After that, I changed my focus
and dug up everything I could...
But you're still
such a mystery...
I am sure of one thing, now...
You are strong and beautiful.
You're practically a god...
You are something far
greater than mankind...
...yet you are not a monster.
Cool!
Well, you are the
star of the show.
The monsters are
just loser extras.
You're the best
protagonist ever!
A star with no script...
Although I guess it
helps that you didn't know
you were in a movie
in the first place.
Good point...
I still don't get
how you could just
like completely forget all
that weirdo stuff you did.
Simple... That decision was made
by the person
behind the experiment.
You were given false memories
and anything necessary was done
to keep you from reverting
back to your original self...
Maintain the farce at all costs.
Would you be the lie
they created for you...
...or would you change...?
Would Saya take
her life back again?
Why the hell would
anyone care about that?
No idea.
Only the creator of this
cruel game can tell you why...
Interesting.
So this is all
about you not wanting
to go along with
the story anymore...
And you needed the three
of us to help you out.
Which explains why you
had us come here to try
and get her memories back
instead of going to Guimauve
where you were told to
just ruffle up her feathers.
Yes.
This isn't gonna
backfire on us, is it?
I mean, coming here?
Of course not.
I'll tell them it was
part of shaking her up...
What's more, I shut off
the camera that
monitors the storeroom.
Nice!
Well played, Miss Tsutsutori!
She's not our teacher;
we can just call her Kanako...
As if that's her real name.
We all had to change
our names, right?
Obviously, yes...
How else could anyone expect
to find so many obscurely
named people all in one place?
Tell me...
What did they promise to
give you in return for this job?
I only wanted to
see the real thing.
And now I have, haven't I?
Yes...
Folklore and mythology
have always been
a source of
fascination for me...
But being able to
experience the truth
was something
I couldn't live without.
I came here for one reason...
And that was to
see it for myself.
To see an authentic Shrovetide,
not this fake one
that they have created.
Okay...
Shrovetide?
What the hell does that mean?
It means... to allow...
And to eat... and crimson...
Basically, it's an
agreement allowing
the beasts to eat humans.
You're kidding... right?
I have spent years searching...
Those small-minded old fools at
the universities made fun of me
for believing it existed,
but that didn't stop
me from looking.
And here it is...
right in front of me.
You're real... Saya...
Real... and those creatures
you call Elder Bairns...?
They're every bit
as authentic as you.
The experiment just won't end...
We should have been
done with it all by now...
This is his doing...
That man...
No, that bastard...
He keeps using
drugs and hypnosis
to force you into staying this
silly Saya Kisaragi character.
I'm sick of it!
Once you're back
to the old you...
I'll make sure you find
the damn Shrovetide for me.
Now, drink...
Drink the blood of the
so-called Elder Bairns.
Come back to me...!
Come back!
Regain your true self!
The tranquilizers work,
but clearly they don't last.
I am relieved they were at least
effective the first time...
Otherwise, even he might not
have been able to catch you...
However...
I certainly can't have
you running around
out of control again.
My apologies...
Don't worry...
I won't take it all.
Your blood is precious...
It needs to be put to good use.
Although... First,
I should give a taste to him...
And the rest...
Well, it's been
promised elsewhere.
Saya... Are you hungry?
I'd like to give you
something to eat.
Well, I guess
the important thing
is we're almost finished
with this stupid job.
Oh, come on...
It hasn't been that awful...
The uniforms are cute.
Yeah, but they're totally out
of place for a high school...
No one would take them seriously
if we were in a real town...
Well, I didn't think
about it that way...
Why do you figure
they designed them
to look like this, though...?
I've never even heard
of black and red uniforms.
Maybe to hide... you know.
To hide what?
All the blood.
Yeah, that makes sense!
When she kills those monsters,
she gets soaked with blood...
This way nobody sees it.
True... Not that it matters;
we're almost done here.
Hey... Do you think they'd
let us take them when we go?
What the hell would
we want these for...?
It'd be like wearing a costume.
Yeah... That's kind
of the idea...
We wouldn't wear them.
Yes! You're a genius...
For the girls, right?
They can put 'em on
when they're working.
We'll be less likely
to get caught...
But, we'll still be
making plenty of money.
Perfect...
We'll be back in business...
Sounds like a plan.
What's going on...?
Her memories
should have returned
after drinking the
Elder Bairn blood...
This is taking far too long.
What?! No way!
Are you all right, Saya?
Your orders were
to report immediately
if there was any
change in the star
so what exactly are you doing?
We know you've been gathering
secretly without checking in...
Evidently, you're
up to something
We didn't do anything.
What do you mean?
Don't play the innocent
card with me, ladies...
The main cast is under
constant surveillance.
Not when we're
off duty, we're not!
That's right...!
Not to mention,
when Saya wasn't around,
we made sure to turn off
our GPS and camera stuff!
Are you kidding...?
You didn't know there
were more than that?
The experiment is
still very much active...
We'd like to know what you're
trying to accomplish here.
They haven't even
killed me off, yet...
Now, look at what
you've done to her...
She's been weakened...
Hurting the star tops the list
of things you're
forbidden to do.
You're overreacting.
We didn't do
anything that bad to her.
Relax.
We didn't tear off
her fingernails.
Or break any of her bones.
You should blame Kanako.
She's the one who told us to.
I did nothing but
tell them the truth!
The cast does not need
to worry about the truth...
That's not our job.
Well, I don't care!
I just wanna go home.
We want this stupid
thing to end, already!
Don't complain now.
You knew what the terms were.
And you agreed
for your own profit.
I didn't agree to near death...!
I want my money!
I couldn't care less
who gives it to me!
Once that thing gets
her memories back,
Kanako said she'd hand my cash
over to me, and I could leave!
But what about our deal?!
He said he wouldn't
just take care
of our last bout with the law...
...he'd completely
expunge our records!
We needed that!
You stupid bitch!
You said nobody
would find out about this.
You lied to us!
How could you even believe her?
The entire town was created
specifically for this project...
The buildings, the people...
Everything you see.
It's impossible to hide
anything in this place...
Impossible.
What is he talking about?
Seriously!
I honestly didn't care
what happened to you.
The bottom line for me
was if we kept this up,
Saya's memories
would never come back.
Experiment, my ass...
He has no intention of
allowing this farce to end!
He overwrites her memory
every time it returns!
If he keeps her like this,
I'll never be able to
reveal Saya to the world!
You what?!
I don't give a damn
about the world...
I've been risking
my life, daily...!
Someone better
give me my damn money!
What the hell?!
If he finds out,
we won't get anything!
Just shut up!
I'm already out of
time with her...
At this rate, I'll be
banned from publishing...
And I have living proof!
She's right here in front of me.
Come on...
Remember who you are,
so he can pay...
He will... I swear!
Oh, will I?
Tell me...
How am I going to pay?
Saya, what do you
believe defines a person?
Does nature define you...?
Or does nurture decide?
Next time on Blood-C:
"If Remembering Me."