It's true. You did
make a promise...
But will you be able
to keep it in the end?
Or... will you break your vow?
It's all up to you, Saya...
The power is in your hands.
Run...! Everyone
get outside, now!
Hurry!
Come on... Stand up!
Hitomi!
This is our chance!
Right now?
Let's go!
Yoshito, no!
This way!
Wait for me!!!
Itsuki! Hurry up!
She's still down there...
How strange...
Why are you angry?
Why...? What?
I asked why you are angry.
How can I not be angry
when you're murdering
all of my friends?
Friends?
I'll... kill you!
Itsuki!
Run for it!
No more... Die!
I can't do this!
I gotta get out of here!
Move! You're in
my way! I said move!!!
To protect them...
I promised... I swore it.
I promised...
I'd protect everyone.
I promised... I...
Saya!
I'm, uh... I am so sorry.
Saya... Who are you?
I am... My name
is Saya Kisaragi...
My father...
is Tadayoshi Kisaragi.
He works as a
priest at the shrine...
And I... I attend
Sanbara High School...
I'm in my second year there.
No!
That's not what I meant.
What are you?
Saya... Saya Kisaragi...
You're here... You survived.
It's dead...
And now... Have you
finally killed them all?
I couldn't protect them...
I couldn't save anyone.
Nene is gone... And Nono, too...
Even Yuka's dead now.
Thank you...
Thank you very much.
I haven't done anything.
You have. I didn't
want to be alone;
and you stayed with me.
Does it hurt?
Yes.
And, where does it hurt?
Is it in your head,
where you think?
Maybe...
The pain is in your body?
Or... do you feel
it in your heart?
There was a great deal
of development today...
The end is near.
To whom did you promise, again?
And, more importantly...
Who are you, Saya?
Think about it...
The truth lies
within the answers.
Also, it might be wise to
consider why you always
have such a difficult time
answering those questions.
Saya!
Tokizane?
What are you doing here?
What a relief?!
You're safe.
I heard what happened at school.
Everyone in class except
for Itsuki is gone...
Including Yuka...
Everyone...
Everyone... Everyone?
What is it?
Tell me something.
Were you...
Were you at school today?
For a bit...
They're saying that some
kind of weird monster showed up.
And what about the school?
Did they call you?
You know, to let you know
they were going to be open?
Yeah.
That message
should have gone out
to everyone, though, right?
What?
The message to come to school...
It would have gone out
to everyone, wouldn't it?
Yeah, I guess it would've.
Then if so... How come
it was just class B?
The only students in the entire
school were from our class.
They were... running away...
But nobody else was
in the halls at all...
I was fighting
the Elder Bairn...
The other classrooms
were empty...
We were the only ones there.
No teachers, even...
Except for Miss Tsutsutori.
I don't understand...
Where was everyone else?
How did you manage
to survive the attack,
and how did you make
it all the way here
after everything
that's happened?
I guess... I was just
worried about you.
You were? Why?
I don't know!
Because I like you.
You're here...
because you like me?
That's right.
But why...?
And when did you
start liking me?
What do you mean...?
I see you in class all the time,
and I like being around you.
You do?
How long have we been in
the same class, Tokizane?
Saya...
Saya!
Why are you here?
It's very late.
Who might you be?
I'm Tokizane...
Saya and I are
in the same class.
Then you should know...
It's far too dangerous for
you to be out at this hour.
Right.
Well...
we can talk more
about this later.
Are you all right... Saya?
My name...
It's Saya Kisaragi...
It is, isn't it?
My name is Saya Kisaragi.
This is my second
year in high school,
and Miss Tsutsutori
is my teacher.
My best friends are Nene...
and Nono... and Yuka.
I'm also friends with Itsuki,
the Class Rep, and Tokizane.
My father is Tadayoshi Kisaragi.
He's a priest at
the local Shrine.
But... I don't... know...
Tell me why...
Why don't I know the
name of my own mother?
My mother's name and face...
I don't remember either one...
How can I not know that?
Saya...
Saya...? Am I really
Saya Kisaragi?
Next time on Blood-C:
"Since 'Tis by Its Breath."