Yikes...!
Now I'm worried about that, too!
But don't sweat it,
if anything was gonna happen...
With my luck,
it would happen to m--
What's going on?!
Look out!
What... What is that thing?!
Saya...! What are we gonna do?!
Stay away from me!
No...! Come back!
Let me go! Let me go!
Nene...! Please come back!
Nene! Come this way!
I need you, but...
You haven't been blessed yet.
Nene!
Saya.
Father...
It killed Nene.
You need to get some rest.
How can I?
Because you must.
Will you find where
the light leads, Saya?
I wasn't dreaming.
It really did happen.
Um, yeah?
Good morning, Saya... It's me.
Why are you here?
May I come in?
Yes, come in.
Tadayoshi told me you haven't
been feeling very well today.
No, I'm fine.
Clearly you're not.
He also said you had a
fever and to convince you
that you needed to stay
home from school today.
But, I...
And, since you're
not gonna be able
to come to the
café this morning...
I brought something
for you to eat.
I'll go warm it up
for you, right away.
But I thought you might
like some coffee first.
Thank you.
Just be careful;
it's pretty hot.
I really appreciate
you coming...
I hope it didn't cause
you too much trouble.
Trust me, it was no trouble.
Please, don't
even worry about it...
You're special to me.
You are more important
to me than anything...
'Kay?
I'll go get your lunch ready.
Try to get some rest
until I come back.
Maybe it's the fever...
My head is so cloudy.
I need to think...
but I can't...
And I'm... So sleepy...
Everything's blurry.
I'm shaking...
Has this happened to me before?
Or was it a dream...?
It wasn't...
It really happened, too.
Let's try it, then...
The two of us...
A dream?
But that place... it seems
so... so familiar to me.
You can stay home again today.
No.
Very well.
Would you mind telling
Fumito I'm sorry I wasn't
able to eat breakfast at
the café this morning?
I'll let him know.
Did the Eight Trigrams
reveal to you
that an Elder Bairn
would appear again today?
Just take it with you, Saya.
I'll be back later.
Please, be careful.
I will.
What's going on?
Oh, hi, Tokizane.
You weren't at school
yesterday, were you?
Uhh... No.
Why? Were you hurt?
I was... I guess...
Not too bad, though.
You can always
talk to me... okay?
Always.
Hey guys, sorry
if I'm interrupting
but class is almost
about to start, so...
Hey... How are you?
I'm fine, thanks.
Well, welcome back;
we missed you.
Saya!
We've all been worried since
you weren't here either.
What do you mean?
Haven't you heard about Nene...?
Nobody has seen or heard
from her in like two days.
Nono's been out of school,
too, because of it.
Take your seats, please.
Yesterday, I told you
Nene Motoe hadn't come home
since leaving school
the day before...
Her parents and the
police are saying
she still hasn't
called or returned.
I'm sure you're all aware...
but several incidents
like this have happened...
And most of them
have been local.
Then it really was true.
What was true?
Everyone's saying people are
randomly disappearing...
They leave to go somewhere and
nobody ever sees them again.
You know they never
did find that baker
we heard about at Guimauve.
You okay?
Nene...
Saya, what's wrong?
Are you all right?
My head... It's hurting.
Are you sure that's all?
She might just still be sick;
she was out yesterday...
Remember?
That's a good point...
Saya, you probably should
have stayed home again today.
Although, at this point
it doesn't really matter;
the police have asked us
to close down the school.
Go straight home and
don't stop anywhere.
Tomorrow morning,
we'll let you know if you
need to come back in.
Make sure you
answer your phones.
Saya?
Um... Yeah?
Take care of yourself.
I made a promise...
I will protect them... Everyone.
Promised whom?
Who said that?
Was it you?
No, that's ridiculous.
Maybe not.
But I could be wrong.
So it was you talking...
Hey, Saya. What's up?
Nene...
I mean... Nono.
Yeah... I'm Nono.
How could you tell?
Everyone else thinks I'm Nene.
I'm not really sure.
Did you know Nene
and I are identical twins?
If I change the part
in my hair to the left,
no one can tell the
difference between us.
So, then...
How did you know it
was me and not her?
I just... I did.
The day she disappeared...
You know where
she said she was going?
To see you...
She said she was worried.
After you collapsed
she started feeling guilty
and wanted to go check
and see how you were.
Saya...
Please, tell me what
happened to my sister!
Nono...
Why hasn't she come home?
Please, just tell me
where she is!
What happened to Nene?!
Say something already!
Why can't you just be
honest with me, Saya?
What happened to her?
Where did she go?
Please, I... Nono...
Why did you do that?
It was mean...!
You're the worst!
I'm sorry.
What was that?
What's going on out there?
What's wrong?
Why are you running
away from me?
Hey... Are you okay?
What's that?!
Nono?
Nono? Nono!
Wake up... Saya.
I am sorry you were
unable to save your friend.
I know it must be painful.
Father...
But understand...
you are the only shrine maiden
we can send to
fight the Elder Bairns.
I am the only one.
Saya...
What will you do
to the Elder Bairns?
Defeat them... I made a promise.
To whom, exactly?
To whom did you make
that promise, Saya?
It's you...
Next time on Blood-C:
"As Pitiless as the Storm."