Saya! What's wrong?
I messed up the omelet...
The end of it got all smushed.
It's okay...
Nothing to worry about,
we'll just have your
father eat that part.
No... You can't do that!
It's fine...
I'll take it.
But you should
have the best part!
Don't you understand...?
He loves everything
you cook so much
he'll eat up every last bite,
no matter how smushed it is...
Right?
Then on this knife I swear...
I'll work hard to give you
what you deserve, Father...
I'm gonna make you the best
breakfast you've ever had!
We thank you for this meal.
The food was good...
I'm so proud of you.
I'm glad you liked it...
Next time I'm gonna
work even harder to try
and make it perfect for you.
Here.
Enjoy, Saya.
Oh... Thank you so much.
Where's Father's?
I'm making it right now.
In that case,
he can have mine first.
That's a nice offer, but
his is different from yours.
Huh?
His is weak...
He doesn't have the stomach
for strong coffee like you do.
Really?
I didn't know that.
It's a fact, to be sure.
Guimauve!
Well, you said you liked it,
so I decided to
make you some more.
Is it okay if
I eat it right now?
Please.
It's so good...
It makes me feel kinda floaty.
Oh yeah...
That stuff's full of sugar.
It's more than
just a sugar rush...
As soon as I put it in my mouth,
I feel light as a feather.
When I have it
with the coffee...
The feeling gets stronger.
Ah, the perfect combo then...
Would you like a piece...?
It's "floaty"...
No. I think I'll pass.
See you later!
♪ Today's great... ♪
♪ It's been lots of fun. ♪
♪ I ate food...
with my dad... ♪
♪ Fumito sure is
a great cook... ♪
♪ It's a perfect
day today... ♪
♪ Guimauve is
my favorite food... ♪
♪ ...and now-I-think-
I'll-go-to-school. ♪
I did it!
Hey wait, don't go that way!
You could get hurt
out here all by yourself...
It's not safe.
What if a car came?
So... You were
running late today
because you were
playing with a dog?
Yes.
Well...
Good for me because
that means I get to have
some help cleaning up
the chemistry room...
Talk about a mess.
This is my punishment...?
You sure there's not
anything else I can do?
No, this is all I need...
Thanks a lot, though...
They're pretty laid
back at this school...
...and I'm just a teacher...
...so I like to go
with the flow.
How long have you
been working here...?
Have you taught at
other schools before...?
I'm sorry to ask so many
questions, I'm just curious.
This is my first
go at teaching...
It's fun.
What did you do
before you came here?
Well, I was a researcher...
Although it was in a
somewhat different field
than the chemistry
I'm doing now.
So you quit to do this, huh...?
That's really neat.
Yep...
That's me...
If I decide I wanna learn,
I'm the type of person
who will do whatever
it takes to succeed.
If you don't mind me prying,
what exactly did
you wanna learn?
Something I could
only learn here...
Teaching at this school...
Enough about me, what about you?
Do you like it here?
It's amazing...!
I have so much fun and all
the people are really wonderful!
Good...
So you're not having issues
with your classmates?
Oh... I see ...
I'm not being rude
or doing anything that's
upsetting people, am I?
The thing is, my
father always tells me...
...sometimes I'm a little--
no, way more
than just a little...!
I'm completely unaware
of what he refers to as
"common sense"...
I've been causing
problems, right?
Not at all...!
Everybody loves you here Saya,
you don't have a thing
to worry about, alright?
Besides...
I like you... and that's
what matters... okay ?
Yes, of course.
So... If you ever wanna talk...
I'm always right here, Saya.
Umm...
Thank you.
Saya, it's you!
Is everything okay?
Today is a half-day, so
we're done with school early...
We should go
somewhere fun after this!
Just give it up, you two!
There's nothing fun
to do in this town...
Idiots.
Yuka is the meanest person
in the history of the world!
Forget her, I wanna
go somewhere anyway!
High school's supposed
to be awesome, isn't it?
Then how come ours sucks?
Nono... Nene...
Please don't cry.
Class rep!
Saya, what's up?
You said you found
a place in town
with really good
cake didn't you?
Yeah, I'm impressed
you remembered.
But you never told
me what it's called.
It's Guimauve.
It's good... Café Guimauve
has the best desserts in town.
Well, the bakery's
not half bad...
Although, the café does
at least serve coffee.
Oh...! It really is
depressing here.
Fun stuff...
Where's all the fun?
As a matter of fact,
I never thanked you
for refusing to go there
with me the first time.
Thank her?
I was just pretending
like I knew the place...
She not only knows it, she
goes there every single day...
If she had said yes,
I would've looked like a moron.
Oh... I get it.
All right! Let's go to
Guimauve and eat cake...!
That sounds like fun, right?
Cake, huh?
Do high school
kids even eat cake?
I guess it's better
than nothing.
Everything Fumito
makes is really good...!
You guys will love this place!
Will you come with me?
You were wrong...
Taking her to Guimauve
would've been a smart move.
Yeah, your guess is
as good as mine...
I never know what
she's gonna say.
It's a perfect day today,
don't you think?
Yeah, definitely.
The weather's all right,
but it's way too quiet.
This town sucks...
Yep... Big time.
You can complain all you
want to, but that's not gonna
make the scenery or the
population any less crappy.
Yeah but--
I don't know, it's so
nice and quiet here.
Don't you understand,
that's why we think it sucks?!
This place is gross...!
Super lame...!
It's a teenage nightmare!
Yeah!
You two...
You always talk in sync!
Like a bad comedy routine.
At least say "like a
pop-star" or something!
Or a big TV star!
I'm sorry, it's just...
I don't get it.
The thing is... I don't really
watch TV.
What?!
Wait, you mean like you don't
watch reality shows on TV?
No... I never do...
We don't own one.
No TV... Like at all?
Yep.
Hold on...
You actually mean
there's no TV in your house?
Yes.
So there's not
one in the den...?
In the bedroom or the
living room or anything...?
None?
Right.
Ew...!
Life without a flat screen!
That's no way
for a girl to live!
Oh, the humanity!
Oh, don't worry; it's
not a big deal at all.
What do you do
when you're at home?
Well, I help out around the
house...
...and... I guess
I read and do my homework.
What do you do for fun?
Father and I talk about stuff...
Oh... and I really love going to
Café Guimauve too,
it's my favorite place!
Oh yeah...!
Come on, let's hurry!
Yummy cakes and hot
coffee are waiting for us!
Oh boy, this is not good.
Well...
Looks like you
brought some company.
It's 'cause your food's so good!
It really is delicious!
Yeah, it's the best!
Well, thank you very much.
You know, I'm not a
big fan of cake usually,
but this stuff is pretty good.
True... It really is tasty.
I'd be interested to
know how you make it.
Why do you ask that, do
you enjoy making cakes too?
Yeah, I love to cook...
and I'm not half-bad.
Oh...? Trying to
win points with Saya?
Is that right?
I guess I'd be lying
if I said I didn't want
to impress her a bit.
What's the matter?
Oh Saya, you're just impossible!
Hey... You know what
would've been lovely?
If Tokizane would have
come had cake with us...
I thought about inviting him,
but I guess he'd already
gone home for the day.
Saya.
Do you think I should feel
bad that she's so upset...?
Or maybe it's better
to ignore it all together.
Sit anywhere you like.
Sorry to be a bother,
but I'm not here to eat.
Oh... What is it?
Well... I just wanted to
let you know the owner of the
Nightingale Bakery has been
missing for over two days now.
The bakery?
There was a closed sign on
the door when we passed it.
Nobody has heard a thing...
His wife tells me it's unlike
him not to make any contact.
Oh my... I hope he's all right.
At this point, we
think it's very possible
something may have
happened to him...
I'm warning
everyone in this area
to be extra cautious
and stay on the look-out.
Thank you for letting
us know, Officer.
And kids... make sure you
get home before dark, okay?
Right.
'Kay!
Thank you!
It can't be.
Another Elder Bairn.
It's elusive...
I could not detect it.
However, one will
surely appear tonight.
Keep your guard up...
It may be different
than the others.
Saya.
It doesn't matter
how strong it is.
I will defeat it,
Father... I swear.
The baker...
Remember...
Honor the covenant...
Do not forsake us.
Human beings evolve...
This may be true, but is
it so very black and white?
Aren't there some
parts that can change
and others that never will?
There's always a fundamental
portion that remains the same.
But imagine...
What if you were to
change at your core?
Would you be the same person?
Surely not, and
more importantly...
"Fundamental change."
Is it truly even possible?
Well, we shall see.
I don't get it, Tokizane...
You can't eat boxed lunches?
I'd rather sleep than eat.
Oh no!
You have to eat;
otherwise, you get sad.
You're an interesting
kid, you know that?
It seems like things
are going really well, huh?
Oh yeah, I'd definitely say so!
Looks like you might
lose your girl, Itsuki.
Don't worry...
I won't let that happen.
Yeah... Me neither!
Huh?
Next time on Blood C:
"That Has Made Me Sad."