You sure about this...?
Seeing you here might
be too much for her.
It's fine... She's too
far gone already...
Right... Saya?
Fumito... What...
So you're back then...
Shame but even giving you
the coffee at this point
wouldn't do you any good.
This isn't how it looks!
I mean, yeah, we might
have made a little mistake...
But it was only
a little bitty one...
If you think about it,
we can't really be
blamed for any of this.
We're just a couple of
kids being kids, you know!
And kids screw up!
It's natural; that's what we do!
Very good point...
I'm not surprised
you see it that way.
Thank you!
Well, here's the
way I see it...!
Give me the money you owe me
so I can get the
hell out of here.
Unfortunately, your actions
are a clear violation
of your contract.
I don't care!
So let me guess...
You're just a kid
being a kid, too?
I don't have any more
time to waste here.
I need to publish and
I need to do it now!
Those brain-dead old bastards
won't give me any more time...
On top of that...
New researchers keep showing up
and taking my grant money...
Those fools...
That damn committee
practically called me mad...!
They laughed at me!
First things first...
You need to take
your hands off Saya.
Saya... Are you hungry?
I'd like to give you
something to eat.
You naturally consume
things similar to yourself...
Similar things that have been
around, for a very long time...
Unlike you, they can
take on different forms...
And those forms
for the most part make
them extremely powerful.
Powerful and rather
hungry for humans...
I happened across their story
in some documents that were...
Well, let's say they
were classified higher
than top secret.
It's called the Shrovetide...
Nothing special, really...
The nation's leaders
made a modus vivendi
with an opponent they
could never defeat...
They allowed a certain quantity
of humans to be devoured...
And in return, they
were promised no more
than that would be killed...
Quite a fascinating
discovery for me.
How so?
For one, those ancient,
heteromorphic
beings intrigued me...
Do you know them...?
Let's call them
Elder Bairns, shall we?
The Shrovetide covenant
was created ages ago...
No one who knows or
handles the agreement now
understands how terrible
these monsters truly are...
Although, how would they?
Do you?
Yes, I'm well aware.
I'm terrified of them...
But, some people
desire to obtain power
because they're afraid of it...
When I was asked
whether or not I could use
the Shrovetide,
what was I supposed to do?
You're lying.
Am I...?
I already have all
the cards I need...
I made sure
to get a hold of him
in order to then
get a hold of you...
After that... Saya...
All I had to do was find you.
You don't feed on humans...
You feed on the blood
of those like you...
The Elder Bairns
fear you because of it.
To them, you're the monster.
Now then, I've prepared food
and a feeding ground for you.
A place with clean air.
Quiet, devoid of outsiders.
Easy to control.
What for...?
What are you planning to do?
Just a little experiment...
Something I wish to discover...
What is that?
I want you to enlighten me...
Humans, by nature, change...
Of course, there are some parts
that modify and
some parts that don't...
But there's a fundamental
core that stays the same...
For example, your abilities,
your strength...
If those remained and we
simply adjusted your birthplace,
your surroundings,
your memories, even...
What would happen?
If all those things changed...
would you still be the
same person as before?
Would you think the same things?
Act the same way?
Or would you evolve
at your deepest level...?
Is it, in fact, possible for
that fundamental core to change?
So what? Why do you care?
You will not escape...
I know what you're thinking;
I can see that
light in your eyes.
I saw the same light
when you fought
my private guards, too...
You were beautiful.
I will not change.
I will not!
We should test it out and see...
Don't you think?
I remember now...
So, this is the stage
and they're the actors for
your experiment, is that right?
Of course.
I did it all for you, Saya...
You swore to me you
would never change...
But I wanted you to...
It seemed we were at
a crossroad of sorts...
So, I decided if we
were going to do it right,
there was going to
be a winner and a loser.
With a prize for the winner...
...and a penalty...
for the loser.
Has the show ended, now?
Like, you know, the grand
finale or whatever they call it?
Oh, yeah!
Her memories are
back so the jig is up.
Hooray, for us!
It's over!
So you don't need us anymore...
We're finished, aren't we?
Absolutely...
If our actors won't
act any longer...
They can go ahead
and leave the stage.
What's wrong with his
talisman, it didn't work!
Yes...
Alas, the ones I gave you after
your first deaths were fake...
They're not going to work.
No, no!
Let me go!!! Let me go! No!
No!
Please, somebody help!
It hurts! Please somebody help!
You're next, Kanako.
I expected your betrayal.
That's why your talisman
has been fake the entire time.
Thanks for your performance.
What weapon she uses
doesn't matter, does it?
Correct...
That nonsense about the shrine
maiden and the sacred blade...?
That was all
just part of the story.
As long as it can draw enough
blood, anything will work.
Save me! Save me!
It's you... Father...
Please, help me; please,
you have to save me!!
Help me!
Looks as though he drank
too much of your blood
this morning, Saya...
I guess you're not the only
one who's back to normal.
You knew what would happen
when you gave it to him.
See, I knew you were back...
How nice.
I assume you know what
he is now... Don't you?
An Elder Bairn...
A half Elder Bairn.
Yes, the result of congress
between a human
and an Elder Bairn...
That's why he has
a human form...
However, his powers...
Well, they're far greater
than a mere human...
He's the closest
being to you, after all.
Which is most likely the reason
you obeyed him so blindly...
Of course the false memories of
his being your father did help.
I thought it was a nice touch.
With the appropriate
suggestions,
your blood controls him...
...in addition to
the Elder Bairns.
So you'd given my blood to
the Elder Bairns I encountered.
I gathered it before
we started this game...
It was the only way I could
force them to do what I wanted.
Appear where I needed them...
Attack people you
thought you love.
If you have control over them...
Why allow so many
innocent people to be killed?
It was more efficient to
have the main cast survive,
but there was
no particular reason
for us to worry about
keeping the extras safe.
Oh, come on, don't
make that face at me...
Humans don't matter to you.
You aren't like them, and you
certainly don't eat them.
You can't do that because
you're under another compulsion.
Not because of me.
I didn't do that to you.
I just used that knowledge
to make the false memories...
You can't kill humans...
That was an arrangement
you had with someone else...
A contract you made.
Yes... To protect
that person from you.
So I promised you
if you were the winner,
I'd make sure you
could kill humans again.
And if I won, well...
Clearly you're not strong
enough as a human to beat her...
Time to change.
Listen to me; you're being
controlled by my blood!
Go back to normal.
Just go back.
Saya.
Tadayoshi.
Did you find where the...
Where the light leads...?
You should know...
Being with you... Saya...
Made me happy.
You were the only one
I ever met like me...
I think that's why...
Hurting you hurt me, Saya...
You were my girl.
Thank you for that.
I'm sorry, Father.
I bet you want to kill
me now... don't you...?
It isn't quite time
for that yet... Not yet...
You won't get away!
Saya!
Tell me why...
I'm not sure...
I was supposed to be
an actor in a silly game.
But then... after awhile...
I think I started to
really care about you...
I couldn't help it.
The one you cared for wasn't me.
No... I suppose not, huh...?
But I know she's still
a part of you... Saya.
Why are they doing this to us?
Who's controlling them?
What is this?!
Hey, let me in!
Let me in! Let me in!
This isn't right!
How amusing...
It appears you're
the only member
of the main cast to survive.
Well, I can't die;
I have goals to accomplish.
You wanted to be
Governor of Tokyo, wasn't it?
Yes, that's right...
It's the only reason I pretended
to be a high school
student for you...
In return...
I'm hopeful you'll help me.
I didn't tell you yet, did I...?
Your beloved guimauve...?
It was made with the
blood of your kills...
I knew you'd enjoy it...
Did you know? Its texture is
said to be like human organs.
Perhaps if you get the
chance to kill me one day,
you can find out for yourself...
Goodbye, Saya.
Before her capture,
Saya made a wish...
She wanted to stay herself...
I granted it, however...
It's time to reach
for the next one.
Saya... Now...
About... That wish...