This place...
Today it's like nothing
ever happened...
What is this?
Saya?
Fumito?
Are you okay?
Oh yeah... I'm fine...
Really, it's just--
It's not nice to lie...
What's wrong?
Look, I know you don't want
anyone to worry about you...
But we can't help if you
keep hiding things from us.
Don't forget...
If you ever wanna talk,
I'm here... 'kay?
To be honest...
I feel a little confused
right now and...
My head...
It feels weird.
Is it hurting?
Yes.
Good news is you don't
seem to have a fever.
I know...
Plus... I don't feel weak...
It's strange, I have no
idea what's causing it.
No caffeine for you then...
I don't think this
is gonna help any.
I'd love some actually...
Your coffee makes
me feel so relaxed.
All right then, if you say so.
Here... Enjoy.
Maybe this is just what I need.
It's good.
Glad you like it.
This is perfect...
I feel so calm...
Like I don't have a
care in the whole world.
She just fell asleep.
I see.
You should know.
She told me she has a headache.
The Elder Bairns
came, didn't they?
Be ready.
Can you do this?
I swear... I'll defeat it.
You are Saya, I presume.
That's one.
Too bad.
I must say I am unimpressed...
I find it hard to believe you're
the one who slew my comrades.
She's gone.
I can't see a thing.
The covenant has
not been honored.
This is the punishment.
Covenant?
Between who...? Tell me!
The humans... and our kind.
What promises were made?
Oh no!
Please...! Help!
Are you okay?
Your face has the
look of a wild hunter.
I swear... You won't touch them.
I'll save everyone
I care about or die trying!
You are wasting your time.
Can you not see?
She's always
one step ahead of me.
What promises were made?
Are you all right?
Covenant...?
Between the humans
and the Elder Bairns?
That dog.
When a human being encounters
that which they can
never understand...
What do they do...?
Naturally, they
search for answers.
They ask themselves questions...
What just happened to me...?
How do I reconcile this...?
What am I supposed to do now...?
Then again the more you
think about something...
Often times, the
further your mind
will lead you away
from the truth...
Yes... Your thoughts will only
get in the way...
...of what your instincts truly
desire, to know the real answer.
Hey, space cadet.
What's wrong with you?
Hey, Yuka.
Are you depressed because
gym class got rained out...?
It's only for one day... Right?
Yeah but...
It's not about the weather.
Really...?
Are you feeling sick?
No, I wouldn't say that...
I'm fine it's just I...
There's so much going on...
So much I don't understand.
Like what?
Well, uh... I'm not sure why,
but my head feels kinda heavy...
I'm in a whole lot of pain,
almost like it's
hurting for me to think.
Tell me what's happening.
Is something bothering you...?
Or are you in trouble?
Whatever's going on,
you can talk to me...
I'm right here.
I mean, come on,
what are friends for?
Yeah.
Listen... up!
Instead of gym class,
we're going to be having
a study hall today!
Scary stories...! Who's got 'em?
Well... It is the perfect
day for that sorta thing.
Yeah!
All right...!
Who wants to go first then?!
That's not a bad idea.
You guys are supposed
to be studying though...
Correct me if I'm wrong,
but I'm pretty sure that's
why they call it "study hall."
Come on; cut us some slack.
How 'bout we compromise:
you can study us
while we tell scary stories.
Where's the educational
benefit in that?
What could it hurt...?
Plus, the class rep was right;
this weather's perfect
for a scary story...
Okay, I'm in!
All right!
But first, you
have to go sit down.
Huh?
That's no fun;
we'd have to do the exact
same thing in a real study hall!
Yeah...
We should at least rearrange
all the seats, right...?
We could set up the chairs
just like we're in a
little tiny movie theater!
Why go to all that trouble?
'Cause...! You see.
We get so scared.
That way we can leap into each
other's arms when we need to!
Those two sure are obsessed
with scary stories, aren't they?
A little bit too
obsessed if you ask me.
Why not...?
This'll be a whole lot more
fun than a study hall...
You can arrange the
chairs however you want...
Wait just a second.
Where exactly do you
think you're going, Tokizane?
Crap.
Slowly, the man
approached the child...
Silently, he moved in close.
He reached out his hand...
And grabbed the
boy by the shoulder.
And then...
The child turned
and faced the man...
He looked at him and said.
"Please, Daddy...
I've been such a good boy,
don't push me off
the cliff this time."
Help!
That's the fakest scream ever!
What a mean
thing to say, Yuka...
Honest, we were really scared!
You circus clowns, saying that
in unison makes it more fake!
That was a great story, huh?
Uh...
I don't get it, why did he take
his own child to the cliff...?
That's dangerous.
Man...
When you're trying
to build the story
to a climax and
no one's paying attention...
It makes you
feel like a big loser.
It's not our fault you told a
story everyone already knows.
Yeah, but couldn't
you say the same thing
about most ghost stories?
Maybe, but...
You've gotta make
it relatable at least...
You know.
"You guys...
This really happened
to my father's ex-wife's
brother-in-law's second cousin
once removed." Or whatev.
That is a very
specific relationship...
I bet you lunch tomorrow
you can't say that twice.
I'd rather hear stories
that happen closer to home.
Like in this town.
Huh?
It's totally scarier if
it feels more real.
That's true, but nothing
ever happens here.
Is that right?
I know a story about this place.
You're like the
best teacher ever!
Hold on...
I don't know about this.
Don't be a baby...!
It's a ghost story, after all...
It's scary, that's
the whole point!
But... what if it
really happened?
Oh, it did.
From what I can tell, it
seems to be a true story...
And according to the legend,
if you hear the ending,
it'll happen to you too.
No way... That's a bit much.
Something will happen...?
You have no idea...
I'm so bored,
every single day...!
Teacher...! You can count me in!
I don't wanna hear any
complaining later...
Got it, Nene?
The story goes like this...
Since days of old, inhuman
things have lived amongst us,
even in this village.
Sometimes...
They take on unusual forms,
very different from a human...
And other times,
for some reason,
they choose to look like us.
But still... These creatures...
They're alike in one respect.
They feed on human beings.
Because they're so all-powerful
and people are
so weak and fragile,
they think of us the
way we'd view an animal.
No matter how dear
someone might be to you...
No matter how
much you love them...
They'd be nothing
to these creatures
but a lesser life-form...
A species that isn't
fit to be anything more
than a source of
food for their survival.
The story goes...
Somehow, the humans
attempted to communicate
with these inhuman monsters...
Because, at least
according to the legend...
A few of these creatures had the
ability to speak our language.
They tried... In the end
though, it was in vain.
In vain...? But why?
Because, from the point
of view of these beasts...
Human beings...?
We are nothing but food to them.
So together...
The villagers...
They came to a resolution.
What was that?
Saya!
Saya?!
Are you all right?
C'mon, wake up...! Hey!
Saya...? Saya!!!
I can't believe
I fainted in class...
It wasn't the thunder, I'm not
scared of stuff like that.
And what did she mean...?
Resolution?
Saya!!!
He actually called me
by my first name...
And it really did seem like
he was genuinely
concerned about me.
I don't know why, but...
Suddenly, something
seems very wrong.
Saya, you there?
Wait, I know that voice.
Hey, Nene!
Hey!
Sorry to keep you waiting!
Oh, I just got here!
But... I'm amazed you
could tell it's me so quick...
Most people couldn't tell the
difference to save their life.
I can see it.
You look the same but
you're different people...
It's obvious.
That totally rocks...!
But when we're not
next to each other,
doesn't it get harder
to tell who's who...?
I couldn't even do that,
and she's my sister!
I don't quite know
how to explain it,
but I can tell you apart...
It seems perfectly
clear to me...
Nono is Nono and Nene is Nene.
Yeah, that's true.
So what's up?
Were you just stopping
by to hang out...?
I've got some homework
to do, but it can wait.
Actually, I wanted
to apologize for earlier...
I feel like the whole
thing was my fault,
I practically begged the
teacher to tell the story.
I just wanted to make
sure you were doing okay.
I'm fine.
Thank you.
Nono was mad, she tried to
stop me and I didn't listen...
I guess I was just wondering
if you were mad at me too.
No way, I'm not mad at you...
As a matter of fact, I think
it's sweet you're concerned.
Yeah but...
I was really worried about you;
you didn't look good.
I'm great...
Other than my head hurting
a little bit, I'm wonderful.
Does it hurt because
you fell down?
Uh, no...
The pain's been
going on for a while.
Yikes...!
Now I'm worried
about that, too...!
But don't sweat it, if
anything was gonna happen...
With my luck, it
would happen to m--
What's going on?!
Look out!
A monster!
Hey there, Saya...
Answer this question:
Do you know which
one of us is Nene
and which one is Nono?
Umm, the one on
the right is Nene
and the one on the left is Nono?
That's right!
Great job!
But how could you tell?
I don't know,
I just know somehow.
Yeah, well what about now?
Riddle me this...
Is one of us the
real Nene or not?
Why are there three Nene's?!
Oh... You'll have to guess.
Next time on Blood-C:
"Dashed by Fierce Winds."