I see...
So you believe time
ultimately defines
what a person will
eventually become...
Fascinating...
Over time, one has
various experiences...
Various interactions
with others...
And these shape the individual.
However...
I do not believe experience
is the complete story...
"Why?" you ask...
I'll show you.
♪ It's so...
nice outside today. ♪
♪ The mountains so high
are pretty and green, ♪
♪ and I'm having
such a good day! ♪
♪ My chores have all been done,
and I didn't sleep too late! ♪
♪ I had enough time to
finish my laundry, too... ♪
♪ Now that I'm out
I'm a little worried ♪
♪ that it might
start raining today. ♪
♪ On the other hand
my father said... ♪
♪ That it would be dry
instead, so it's all okay. ♪
♪ It will be okay. ♪
It'll be okay, huh?
Fumito?! I didn't see you there!
Oh...
I'm so embarrassed.
Well don't be...
That was a cute song.
♪ Ya da da. ♪
♪ Father said that it
would be dry instead. ♪
♪ So it's all okay. ♪
Please stop!
Your father's even showing up
in your songs now, isn't he.
Well, yeah, but it's
for a good reason.
When he says it won't rain...
it never does!
He's right...
It will be okay!
You sure that isn't just
because he checks out
the weather reports
every morning?
It doesn't matter; he's still
never been wrong about it,
and I ask him every day!
You really do love
him a lot, don't you?
Yes!
For you.
What is it?
It's a reward.
You know, for getting
all your laundry done.
And your chores too.
You heard the
laundry part, too...?
I must have been
singing so loud...
This is awful.
I have to say, your voice
is surprisingly lively.
Go on and eat it...
It's called guimauve.
That's the same
name as your café.
Yep...
That's right.
You like to drink your
coffee black, don't you?
Yeah.
I just think it tastes
better that way.
I have to drink the
coffee you make here
at least once a day;
otherwise, I feel weird.
Glad you like it...
...and... the two should
go well together.
It has kind of an
unusual texture.
In a bad way?
No, it's great!
Good answer!.
That's what I was
hoping you'd say!
I can't believe how yummy it is!
You know, I thought
those little cakes you had
my father bring me not too
long ago were pretty tasty, too!
You liked those, huh?
Yes! I like any kind of sweets!
You probably didn't
know this about Tadayoshi,
but he's got a
sweet tooth himself.
Really?
I had no idea; he's never
eaten snacks with me.
He must be embarrassed.
Oh, well, should I not
have a sweet tooth then?
Is it something that I need
to be embarrassed about?
Not at all...
You are perfectly adorable.
But then...?
Adult men don't like to admit
they've got a thing for sugar...
It's not necessarily
the most masculine trait.
Are men not supposed
to eat sweets?
Oh no...
But I'm guessing
Tadayoshi thinks
he's cooler than
a sweet tooth...
And he wants you
to think so, too.
That doesn't make sense.
I already do think he's cool.
I'll be sure to tell him that...
And, while I'm at it,...
I'll let him know
it's too late...
You know about his love of
all things saccharine already.
Guimauve!
Take it.
You mean, this is for me?
Of course.
Wow, thank you!
♪ Guimauve, guimauve... ♪
♪ I think it
tastes wonderful. ♪
♪ It's mysterious and so
sweet, and it's fluffy, too. ♪
You know, they say
guimauve's texture
feels a lot like something else.
What is it?
Good question.
I wonder what that
something else could be.
What does it feel like?
Good morning, everyone!
What held you up today?
A dog.
You saw another abandoned dog?
Not exactly;
it wasn't abandoned...
just alone.
Wouldn't that make
it abandoned, then?
No... I don't think so;
it was pretty calm
for the most part
and acted like it knew
precisely where it was
and what it was doing.
Was it like a big dog?
No...
It was small.
A puppy?
No, full grown;
he was just small.
His fur had this really
weird pattern on it.
Weird like how?
Oh...
Good morning,
Class Rep, how are you?
Good, thanks...
If you started using my actual
name, I'd be better, though.
Does that mean you want me
to call you Class Rep
Tomofusa from now on?
Uhh... No, that's not
what I was saying.
Oh no!
Itsuki's pitch goes wild!
And Saya doesn't even
know she's supposed to play!
When they're this
good at ignoring you,
it makes you want to get their
attention that much more.
We believe in you, Itsuki!
It's time for class, guys.
Late again Tokizane?
Sorry about that.
That apology of yours barely
keeps you out of trouble, too.
Morning, Tokizane!
Impressive.
That looks good...
D'you make it?
No, Fumito made it for me...
He's a great cook.
Who's Fumito?
Café Guimauve?
You've heard of it, right?
Of course I've heard of it.
It's the only café in town.
It's also the only place
that even remotely
resembles a coffee shop.
Fumito owns the café.
You must know him
pretty well for him
to make you fancy
lunches like that.
I guess so; he went to the same
high school as my father did.
Really?
That's kind of surprising...
He seems like he's a
lot younger than your dad.
He is.
Apparently, they didn't
attend at the same time.
Well, that explains it.
Way to break that ice, Itsuki!
You like totally still
have a shot with her!
Well, thank you... I'm trying.
Hey, guys...
Do you know what guimauve is?
You mean like, the cafe?
No... The candy.
Oh yeah...
The one that kind of looks
like a pink marshmallow?
What about it?
Have you tried it before...?
I heard its texture feels
just like something else.
I don't know; I've never had it.
I have.
Me too!
So, what do you think
it feels like, then?
It's just like a kiss!
A what?
Saya, you know what
a kiss is, don't you...?
Yeah... I sorta figured saying
that would freak her out.
You can do it, Itsuki!
Well, thank you...
I'll keep at it, I guess.
If you don't hurry up and eat,
lunch will be over
before you finish.
Oh, yeah.
That's so cool.
Yeah, it is.
I wish we had a homemade lunch.
What are you girls eating today?
Bread!
It's from the
Nightingale Bakery.
I love the bread from there...
All their stuff is so good!
Which is helpful; it is
the only bakery in town.
Yeah, if it wasn't good,
we'd starve to death.
This place has got
just one of everything.
There's even only one
supermarket.
Come on, there's more
than one of some things.
Like what?
Like places to hang out.
Quit complaining.
It's not like we
have a choice...
This is more of a village
than a town, if you ask me.
Yeah, there aren't
many people here...
It's practically abandoned.
That's the truth.
But it's really great here...
Nice and quiet.
Uh, seriously...?
You like it... here?
Yeah!
Hey, Saya!
Excuse me!
Tokizane!
Hi... Are you hungry?
Sorry?
Have you eaten?
No... Not yet.
If you don't hurry up and eat
something, lunch will be over.
Yeah, wellI'm not hungry.
You should still eat.
Why's that?
Because you have to...
Otherwise you'll get sad.
Try this!
No thanks.
Do you like it okay?
Yeah... it's good.
Thank you!
What a relief?!
I don't get it.
Why are you thanking me?
Well, for starters you ate it.
Also...
You were complimentary...
And then that made me happy!
She is ridiculous.
Oh no...
You think she likes Tokizane?
I don't know, but technically,
they did just
have lunch together.
Hey... I hope that doesn't scar.
Saya!
Stop standing
there like an idiot.
We're almost done eating;
move it or lose it.
Right, sorry!
♪ No surprise. ♪
♪ It stayed nice out today. ♪
♪ The sky it glows ♪
♪ and it turned out just
like Father said it would. ♪
♪ Now I get to go home and
my laundry's already done. ♪
♪ Everything's okay! ♪
♪ No surprise. ♪
♪ It all turned out just
like Father said it would. ♪
♪ Everything's okay. ♪
♪ Yes, it's o-kay. ♪
Father!
I'm back; did you
have a good day?
Yes, I did... Saya...
Yes?
I'm glad you're so cheerful...
...but that song
you were... singing...
Don't tell me you heard me, too?
Uh... Yes.
You went to the archive today?
I did.
Were you looking
for something specific?
I was trying to find the one
who named them Elder Bairns.
So far, I haven't been able to
find it in any of the books...
However, based upon entries
I have repeatedly uncovered
throughout the documents,
these creatures
have been feeding on
humans for a very long time.
They've been feeding on humans?
You're the only
one fighting them...
So you know this
better than anyone...
They are incredibly strong.
Yes.
And you also know
the only thing capable
of defeating these evil beings.
The sacred blade.
Correct.
Your mother fought
the Elder Bairns
using the sacred
blade as well, Saya...
She fell to them.
I won't fail... I promise.
I'll defeat them.
I swear Father...
I'll protect everyone.
I will protect them.
Oh no! I was
finally late to school!
Let me guess; you were
up late watching TV?
The news or a comedy
show or something?
The shopping channel
or a documentary?
A variety show or
a singing show?
A travel show or a cooking show?
Um, I'm not entirely
sure what those things are.
The Kisaragi family
secret is finally revealed...
What could the
shocking truth be?!
This is lame.
Next time, on Blood-C:
"As for Man."