What, do you believe,
defines a person...?
Not a flesh and blood
embodiment of self, per se...
Yes, physical form is
of course a piece of
this fascinating puzzle...
However, what I am
attempting to uncover
is something further
beneath the surface.
Something more often referred
to as a person's "character"...
Is one's individuality, perhaps,
determined at their birth,
by hereditary traits...?
Or, rather, are a person's
innate qualities created
by their upbringing...?
Does nature define you...?
Or does nurture decide...?
I suggest we try a
little experiment...
One day I will
catch the light...
Soon...
And then I will
find out what it means.
Saya.
Hello, Father!
Are you all right?
Yes, I'm fine; don't worry...
I'm really tough.
I know how strong you are...
Yet still...
A shrine maiden should try not
to smash her head
into things so often...
Do you understand?
I do, but I don't
always hit my head ...
Do I?
Saya... listen to me...
This is important...
You must learn to
be more careful,
and not only with your head.
I understand, Father...
I'm sorry.
Well...
Perhaps it speaks
to your concentration...
Your rituals?
Finished...
I saw that light
again this morning.
Did you catch it?
No, sir...
I did try...
But it got away.
You should not give up...
Have you been seeing
it more frequently?
Yes...
I almost feel as though
I remember it from somewhere.
Almost...
I 'm not sure, though.
Your mother was a
shrine maiden as well...
She often received auguries
between the real world
and that of dreams.
Pay attention;
what you see may contain
some portent of the future.
Maybe finding it out will
help me fulfill my duty.
There is no need
to force anything...
But you might
learn from this light
Yes, sir...!
If I do, I'll let
you know immediately!
One more thing, Saya...
Yes, Father?
If you plan on going
next door for breakfast...
I suggest you change your
clothes as quickly as you can
and make your way over there.
Well, I was wondering what
happened to your nose...
The tip of it's a
little scratched up.
Father's right.
I'm too careless.
I need to focus better.
True...
I think, at times,
you can be a little hasty.
I just wish; I wish I didn't
cause my father so much trouble.
That works both ways, Saya...
I know your father, remember...?
And, he doesn't exactly make
things easy for you, either.
He is tough...
But he's also really
kind, and honest...
He's, well... wonderful!
Ever the daddy's little girl...
You do love him
a lot, don't you...?
Yes...!
So much...
I wish I could do
more to help him...
But I feel like I'm still so
inexperienced at everything.
Now, that's not true...
You should give
yourself a break.
You're doing your best.
Hey... Isn't it
time for school...?
Hold on!
You have ten minutes
to get there...
Take your time, okay?
Don't trip!
♪ Oh, it's so...
nice outside today. ♪
♪ The sky is clear, ♪
♪ so blue and clear. ♪
♪ The sky is clear,
so blue and clear. ♪
♪ Toast and eggs
for breakfast, ♪
♪ and my favorite coffee... ♪
♪ I am feeling great
this morning. ♪
♪ What a pretty day! ♪
♪ It's so...
nice outside today. ♪
♪ I woke up right on time ♪
♪ and I did my chores, too. ♪
♪ Butterflies fluttering, ♪
♪ and the ants
are doing what they do... ♪
♪ Oh, I'm feeling
great this morning. ♪
♪ What a pretty day! ♪
♪ It's so...
nice outside today. ♪
♪ I feel likeI am about to
drift off and float away. ♪
Good morning, everyone!
Look who got here on time.
Yeah, barely...
It was close.
No more lost children today?
No old ladies needing
your help crossing the street?
No, but...
But I did find some trash
left on the ground, so...
Tell me you did not pick up
someone's disgusting crap.
How could I not?
I left it where they
usually pick up the trash...
...but... you know what...
I think the garbage trucks
had already come by.
At least it's picked up.
What's wrong with you?
Think about it...
You are like the
biggest sucker ever...
Every morning some new
ridiculous thing makes you late.
But I wasn't even
a little late today.
I'm not talking about today.
I'm referring to the two times
a week you usually are late!
I'm sorry, Yuka.
What good does it do
to apologize to me?
Yuka can be so scary!
She's like a mean,
overprotective mom!
Shut your mouths!
I, uh...
I hate to interrupt but...
Oh, Class rep!
Our teacher is almost here.
Sorry; I hope
we weren't too loud.
No. Don't worry.
I actually like watching
your little routine.
Trust me.
Don't be stupid.
And every comedic team
needs its straight man.
Who you callin' a straight man?!
You...! He means you!
Okay, it's nice to
see you having fun,
but it's time for class.
We can catch up
with the rest of your
little routine during lunch.
This is not a routine!
And isn't it always
like the straight man
to get so easily offended?
Welcome, Tokizane...
Can't you pretend
to care you're late?
I'm late; sorry.
Well, that was
thoroughly convincing.
Thank you.
Now then...
Since we all seem to be here,
why don't we take attendance?
Kisaragi... Saya.
Yes, I'm here!
All done! Just kidding.
Ha! Miss Tsutsutori,
you're always so funny!
You're so cool!
Saya's the best in school!
Well, thank you;
that's really sweet.
They're right, you know.
Unbelievable.
Were you born this way or what?
Well, I've always been
good at sports and stuff.
Do you have like a million
first place trophies at home?
Your parents must be so proud!
Not really.
My dad is a priest,
so he's busy with that...
My mom died, so it's just us.
We're sorry.
Don't be; you don't
have to apologize.
We're perfectly happy.
My mother passed away back when
I started elementary school,
so I don't remember her much...
Luckily, father
and I have Fumito!
He started making
me boxed lunches
and was really supportive.
He's owns the café next
to the shrine, right?
Yep... Neither one of us cook...
So he's been kind
enough to step in...
He usually makes
most of our food
and brings it to
the shrine for us.
That's cool...
You're lucky, Saya.
Your dad and that Fumito guy
seem like super awesome people.
Yeah!
Hey, Saya...
Oh, class rep!
I was wondering, uh...
Wanna walk home with me?
I thought we
could stop for cake...
I know a good place.
Wow, thanks for the offer...
But there's a ceremony
at the shrine tomorrow...
I promised to go home after
school to help my dad out.
O-kay... Next time.
Sure thing...! Now I'm sad...
I'm missing out on
some yummy cake.
Well, not just cake.
What do you mean?
I uh... Nothing.
Be careful on your way back.
I will!
You be careful too.
Thanks for the offer.
Bye...
Saya?
Are you leaving already?
Yeah!
I'll see you tomorrow!
A doggie!
No!
I have to go home!
Father!
Is it time?
My time?
Come with me.
The signs indicate an Elder
Bairn will appear tonight.
According to the Eight Trigrams?
An omen appeared when
I cast the Trigrams earlier
in preparation for the ceremony.
I see...
Slay it... Saya.
Turn on my soul...
My awareness...
Help me confirm
their infinity...
May the first god
grant me wisdom.
May the land god
grant me strength.
Saya.
Father!
Have you been hurt?
No, I'm fine.
I slew the Elder Bairn,
just like you said.
I know... Well done, Saya.
Come... let us purify
the sacred blade.
Yes.
Are you all right, child?
Yes, I...
My hand.
I see... You must have
been gripping it too tightly.
Saya?
Yes, I'm fine...
It's nothing.
I've already heated
the water for you...
Go take a bath.
Yes, yes father
Good morning!
I made it to class on
time again today...!
I'm not late to school
all the time or anything,
but if I see someone
who needs help,
or a puppy or stuff like that,
I just can't stop myself...
You know, now
that I think about it,
I wonder if that little dog
I ran into would be my friend.
I bet one day it will let
me pick it up and hug it.
Oh, I just know it will!
And until it does,
I won't give up!
Next time on Blood-C:
"It Is for Thy Sake."