What happened?
Talk to me, Saya.
Are you okay...?
Is that your blood?
No, it's not.
It 's...
What are you doing?
I'm so relieved...
When I first saw you here...
I was worried you might be hurt.
Let's go.
Okay but... Where?
Thanks for being so nice to me.
Saya...
What was that?
Why are you carrying that
sword with you everywhere?
Well, I--
Please... Tell me.
I can't... If you
get involved...
Then you'll be in danger,
and I don't want anything
bad to happen to you.
I'll be fine, you're the one
I'm really worried about.
I wanna know everything.
You do...?
How come?
What, you can't tell?
No, I guess not.
Guess the subtle
approach won't work...
Well... that's okay...
I'll just lay it out there.
In my eyes... you're special.
Don't you see?
You're everything to me...
You're it.
And you can talk to
me about anything...
Who knows?
Maybe there's something
I can do to help.
If I tell you this
you have to swear...
You have to promise
to keep it between us.
I will.
Good... Then I'll tell you.
Morning...
Saya ate her breakfast
before she went to school.
I see.
But... she looked
sad... Very sad.
Sad, eh?
Yes...
She's probably worried
that she's upset you...
Or, that you might be
disappointed in her...
Lovely child...
She really does care
about her father a lot.
I suppose it's true: blood
does run thicker than water.
Would you like some coffee?
No.
Oh... Well... Would you
prefer something else?
They're called Elder Bairns?
So what...?
They survive by like
eating human beings?
Yes. First Nene... Then Nono...
And the rest of the
missing people, too.
You know it's not
your fault, right?
Yeah but...
I'm supposed to
fight the Elder Bairns,
and protect the people I love.
I made a vow to defeat them...
To do everything I can--
What's wrong?
It's all right,
I'm fine... Please.
It doesn't look that
way to me, Saya.
Tokizane?
I'm here.
I don't get it...
Why are you
holding me like this?
Come on... You know...
You have to know...?
It's so clear.
What's the matter?
Is there something
wrong with me?
No, not wrong, I mean...
It's just the way
you are... For now.
I believe everything you said...
I know you're
telling the truth...
I saw the monster for myself...
That's all that matters.
No.
Huh?
Uh... I mean...
It's not a monster, it's...
It's an Elder Bairn, that's all.
That's a weird distinction
to make, don't you think?
I'm not sure, maybe.
Aren't those two
things one and the same?
Yeah... I guess they are.
From the looks of you,
I'd say you need a bath...
I don't think a
handkerchief's gonna cut it.
I'll walk you home
so you're safe...
Come on.
No, I'm good, really.
No, you're not.
Yeah, but--
Really... You should
let me help you.
I can carry that.
Please, I'll get it...
Your sword.
Thank you...
I'm very lucky you're here.
Such a gentleman.
Umm... Tokizane?
What's up?
You're a really great guy.
What're you talking about?
Nothing, it's just...
I wish everyone
understood you...
I wish they all could
see how nice you are.
You know.
That's all that matters.
Yeah, but that's such a waste!
Unfortunately,
I gotta take off...
But... if anything's bothering
you at all, just tell me.
So you really want
me to... tell you?
Sure.
But why?
Cause I wanna know you...
Everything about you.
That means so much!
Father?!
Where are you?
Father!
What happened to you?!
Talk to me!
Father!
It's you.
You're awake!
You're gonna be okay...!
What's wrong,
were you feeling sick...?
It's my fault...
I didn't even know.
I'm fine...
Just dizzy, that's all.
Yeah but...
You look really pale
and-- That's blood!
Oh no, did I get it on you?
Please, it's nothing.
No, you're--
You need to calm down...
Saya...
Don't worry about me,
I'll be all right.
You'd tell me...?
If you weren't...?
Yes.
Do you mean it...?
You promise me you would?
You have my word...
I'll be fine.
I'm so glad...!
If anything happened
to you, I swear I'd...
I swear I'd... I don't know.
I can't think
of anything to say.
What would I do...?
If you were gone?
Father.
I wonder why he wouldn't
tell me what was wrong with him.
♪ If Father's sad,
then I am sad as well. ♪
♪ If he's blue, then I am blue
though the sky's blue too. ♪
♪ I... love him. ♪
♪ And he loves me too.
And he loves me too. ♪
But what if he's not
telling me the truth...?
Oh no... What if he's not okay?!
I've gotta find out!
Well, hello...
It's you again.
Yep, it's me...
I have to say,
I'm relieved
you're not screaming
your head off right now.
You're hurt.
The wound's almost closed up.
Whadda you make of it?
Come on...
You don't find it strange
that your body heals so fast?
I never really thought
about it before.
Okay , I guess that
was a stupid question.
So... Do you remember
whom you promised...?
Have you thought about it?
Oh, no...
I can't remember anything.
Well...
Have you considered what
would happen if you broke it?
To put a stop to
the Elder Bairns...
To protect everyone.
If you were to
break that promise...
...what would happen to you?
This experiment is extremely
important to both of us.
If we go through with it...
We'll need a means
to decide who won.
That requires a reward
for the victorious party.
And for the loser?
A punishment.
Saya.
If you win, what would you like?
And if you lose...
What could I take that would
be more painful than death?
Your move.
Don't you pass out...!
I can't carry you like this...!
Keep it together now.
I knew it wouldn't be
easy for you to remember.
It's close... The time has
almost come.
It's weaker...
You're nearly there.
Saya...! What's wrong?!
Uh... I'm okay...
I'm almost done in here.
Punishment...?
A reward?
It's been three days now...
And still no sign
of the Elder Bairns.
Yes.
People from the school
notified me earlier today;
they are planning to
resume classes at once.
I understand.
Will you go?
Yes...
I have to.
Are you all right?
My dear child...
Tell me... Does it
cause you any pain...?
Fighting them
all by yourself...?
Being alone...?
Knowing you are the only one?
My wounds heal very quickly...
Besides, I'm tough;
I don't mind a little pain!
Father... You don't seem well.
No, I... I'm fine,
really... Trust me.
What did the eight
trigrams show you...?
Look, whatever you saw,
it doesn't matter,
because I'm not afraid
of the Elder Bairns...!
There's no need for you
to be worried, all right...?
What happened to Mom won't
happen to me, I promise you!
I'll be fine!
Father, talk to me.
Saya... I...
When the Elder Bairns appear,
remember your vow...
Destroy them and
return home to me.
Understand?
Saya?
Good morning, Yuka.
Hey, what's the matter...?
You don't look so good.
No, everything's great.
Well... I suppose
that's something...
After all this,
it's nice to know
somebody's looking
at the bright side.
They still haven't
found Nono or Nene...
And did you hear
about the policeman?
Apparently, a few days ago,
he went missing too...
I don't know what's going on,
but I hope they're
all gonna be okay.
You're here!
Oh, hello.
With school being
closed for so long,
I feel like I haven't
seen you in forever.
Yeah.
I'm definitely glad
to see you again...
But I'm sorry it's happening
at a time like this,
I wish it wasn't.
What's that?
You brought it here last
time, too... Didn't you?
This is, uh--
Hey, what's up?
What're you screamin' for? Whoa!
I wanna see!
That's one ugly mother!
No kidding man,
look at that thing.
No, not here!
What is it?
I don't know.
Oh, no... It's coming this way.
Eh, I wouldn't worry,
it looks kinda slow.
But it sure is creepy.
Guys! Get down!
What the hell's going on ?
Where did he go?
They're... They're dead?
Come on guys...! Lets go!
This monster, it's not letting
anybody get out of here.
Help me!
Saya?
Saya, no!
Just stay back!
This ends right now,
you hear me? Now!
I will not let anyone else die!
Who are you? Tell me the truth!
My name is
Saya Kisaragi... My father...
That's not what I meant!
And now... Have you
finally killed them all?
Next time on Blood-C:
"Against My Wish."