[TOKUGAWA]
Sanada. Tell me something.
Regarding Mitsunari.
Does he still despise me?
[ISHIDA]
You are the one from that day.
Yes. That day at Odawara.
I'm the man who lost to you.
[ISHIDA]
Hmph.
And what brings that man
to stand before me now?
Have you come to be
defeated once more?
[DATE] Go on, get the
snark outta your system.
I ain't here for revenge or
anything stupid like that.
I just had a little
somethin' to say to you.
Well, to myself, actually.
Call it a statement.
You're just a bump in the road.
In other words...
I'm tellin' you "go to hell."
You see?
[ISHIDA] Your idle words
do not concern me.
However, if you mean to bar
me from my path to Ieyasu,
I will make it so you can never
open that yap of yours again.
[DATE]
Fantastic.
I'll have you know,
this guy here...
is deadly!
This is your punishment
for aligning with Ieyasu!
I will slice you down
to a one eyed snake!
Ha. Well, if you're gonna
be a dick about it!
[yelling]
[ISHIDA grunts]
Lord Masamune.
[DATE] Ooh. Nice to see you're
just as good as I remember.
[SHIMAZU] Ha, ha, ha! Some
right interestin' things
are gettin' started down
there, too. [laughs]
[OTANI]
Are you sure you should be here?
Brave Katakura,
who declares himself the
Right Eye of the Dragon?
[KATAKURA grunts]
Are you worried about Ishida?
You can drop the
provocations, Otani.
My only duty is to do the job
that I've been entrusted with.
And besides.
As he is now,
Lord Masamune is strong!
[DATE]
Hmph.
[OTANI]
You are quite confident.
[KATAKURA] This battle
is a line Lord Masamune
resolved to draw in
order to move forward.
The Dragon will race
across the heavens.
And I'm not going to let anyone
get in the way of that!
[OTANI chuckles] A dragon that
races across the heavens?
Funny you should say that.
[OTANI] Before he goes racing
across the heavens, how about I,
take out his right
eye here and now?
[KATAKURA grunting]
[OTANI]
I despise this world!
People lie, deceive,
and ridicule.
[OTANI] I have seen it
time and time again.
Behold those stars.
[OTANI]
Even in their brilliance,
there is inequality.
In that case, people
and those glittering stars
can all fall to the ground.
And have misery bestowed
upon them in equal measure.
What?!
[OTANI]
It will be Mitsunari and I
who bring about that
world of equality!
Now, you star scraps,
come raining down,
tumbling out of the sky!
[OTANI laughs]
[KATAKURA]
So, Otani,
this was your intent
from the very beginning!
[OTANI]
Soon, my boy.
Very soon!
[KATAKURA gruns]
[OTANI] Soon, equal misery
will fall upon us all.
It will come from the far
reaches of the sky!
Streaming along!
Wave after wave!
[OTANI laughs]
[OTANI]
Katakura.
Can you not see it?
[KATAKURA]
Uh.
[KATAKURA grunts]
"Equal misery," you say?
[OTANI]
Yes!
Misery shared with all,
across the world!
For me as well?
[OTANI]
For you as well.
[KATAKURA]
And for yourself?!
[OTANI]
And for myself!
[KATAKURA]
For my Lord Masamune?
[OTANI]
Yes, for the One-Eyed Dragon!
And Ishida?
[OTANI]
Mitsunari?
No, not him.
I shall allow no more misery
to befall Mitsunari!
[OTANI gasping]
[KATAKURA] You may be capable
of deceiving others, Otani.
But it seems you cannot
fool your own heart.
In fact, right at this moment,
you are the kindest man alive.
[OTANI exhales]
[OTANI]
M... M... Mitsunari.
Just what I expected, Tadakatsu!
Yer bein' known as
the warrin' states'
greatest warrior's no lie!
What fun this is!
[TOKUGAWA]
Tadakatsu.
I killed Lord Hideyoshi
with my own bare hands.
With these hands.
With my own strength.
No gettin' distracted now!
I'm an ol' fool,
behind the times,
I only know how to make war.
So I'm awful grateful to've
met up with ya here.
I'm gonna put all my
might behind this sword
and I want ya to fight it!
Here's a Shimazu
Jigen Style strike!
[SHIMAZU]
Toriya!
Ah!
T'was such a fine fight!
Damn!
Doesn't that pseudo-sun
have any dead angles to it?
[MORI] My Sun has no such
things as dead angles.
All movements thus far and
the course of this battle
have gone just as I predicted.
Here, upon Sekigahara,
it will be neither the
East nor the West,
but the land of Aki
to emerge victorious.
Once this matter is concluded,
I will become its divine oracle.
[CHOSOKABE growls]
You killed my sons-of-bitches,
you used me, and spurred Ishida
on to make a broken mess of
the land of the rising sun!
And that was all for yourself?!
You won't get away with it.
Mori, you're the one guy
I'm gonna make sure
doesn't get away!
[MORI chuckles]
Pathetic fool.
You have no sea, no
ship at your command.
You are run aground.
[CHOSOKABE growls, gasps]
[ALL gasp]
Damnation!
Miserable, overly
sentimental pirate.
Meet your death,
lost and wandering.
Son of a...!
We're screwed, Captain!
There's nowhere left to run!
We're like fish in a barrel!
So it's a trap. then?
I'll show him a trap!
We just gotta soak up that
pain-in-the-ass sunlight
and then throw it back
at the dumb bastard!
[CHOSOKABE SOLDIERS gasp]
[CHOSOKABE]
Heave-ho, ya sons-of-bitches!
[CHOSOKABE SOLDIERS]
Aye-aye, Captain Chosokabe!
[MORI]
Hm?
Hmph.
Impressive, but futile.
Fire all rays at once!
[gasps]
[CHOSOKABE chuckles]
Land, ho!
[CHOSOKABE SOLDIERS cheer]
[MORI SOLDIERS scream]
[MORI growls]
Curse you, Chosokabe.
My sun mirror!
[ALL]
We did it, Captain!
Wa-hoo!
My lost sons-of-bitches,
I'll have my revenge!
[MORI growls]
[CHOSOKABE yells]
[CHOSOKABE]
Damn you, Mori!
Know that each of these blows,
holds the spirit of my
sons-of-bitches who died!
Their spirit?
You've allowed hatred
to blind you,
yet you deign to
speak of spirit?
The fault lies entirely
with your own foolishness.
[CHOSOKABE] Yeah, guess
I gotta live with that.
But know this.
I'm gonna beat you here.
Go to the gravesite of my
sons-of-bitches to report that,
and look after all
your men, too.
And that'll be it.
After that, I'm just gonna
forget all about you.
What?
[CHOSOKABE]
Heh. This'll sound corny,
but I got help from a
lot of different folks
to get to where I am now,
and that opened up my eyes.
[MORI]
Hollow inanity.
Mm?
[CHOSOKABE]
Call it what you will.
I'll never forget
the sons-of-bitches
you took from me.
And even if I die, my crew
will remember their captain.
But when you're dead and gone,
no one'll be remembering you.
[MORI growls]
What was that?
[CHOSOKABE] Even if you were to
seize the country using whatever
ploys you've got, I'm saying
that no one'll talk about you.
[MORI growls]
[CHOSOKABE]
That's how you live your life.
A solitary soul!
And solitude's a thing
that goes on forever,
even after you're dead!
You're a bastard.
You dare to speak
of me in this way?!
[MORI yells]
I have not erred in
any way whatsoever!
Not strategically
and not in my life!
Not in any way!
Looks like when your temper
gets the better of you,
you grow inattentive to
your surroundings, too.
[MORI]
Silence!
[MORI yells]
[CHOSOKABE yells]
Ready, sons-of-bitches?
'Cause here we go!
[CHOSOKABE SOLDIERS]
Aye-aye, Captain!
[gasps]
[CHOSOKABE]
Goodye, Mori.
I hope you find regret
in your damn solitude.
[MORI gasps]
[CHOSOKABE] I'd say my
business here is done.
[CHOSOKABE]
Now about Ishida and Ieyasu.
Lord Masamune.
[ISHIDA, DATE grunting]
y only objective
is Ieyasu's head!
You are no more than wild
grass on the roadside!
Heh. Wild grass?
Come on.
Don'tcha know how hard
weeds are to get rid of?
[DATE groaning]
[ISHIDA] So you lost one
little skirmish against me.
What of it?
That day, I tasted
eternal defeat!
[DATE]
Toyotomi's death, right?
And what did you do to
honor his sacrifice?
Blame someone?
Hate everyone?
[ISHIDA]
Silence!
What could you possibly
know about me?
[DATE] You're right,
I don't know squat.
Thing is, I came
to a realization.
And that new insight
might be the thing
that makes Sanada and
me better than you.
[ISHIDA]
What?!
That's why...
you can't win against me!
I care nothing about you people!
Now be gone!
[gasps]
[DATE yells]
[ISHIDA groaning]
Why?!
Why does my blade
refuse to reach him?
[DATE] You showed me how
far I still had to go.
And for that,
I'm grateful to you.
Most importantly you reminded
me I still got the Right Eye
of the Dragon by my side.
[ISHIDA] Your drivel
does not interest me!
Now die!
[DATE grunts]
[ISHIDA grunts]
What the...?
[DATE grunts]
[ISHIDA growls]
[ISHIDA gasps]
Why do you not kill me?
Is this what you call mercy?!
[DATE] Heh. I told ya, I didn't
come here to take your life.
Just to settle an old
score for myself.
[ISHIDA gasping]
It's the end of
judgment, my man.
And the verdict's in for
guys like you and me.
But Ishida, you dragged
the whole land
of the rising sun into
this big-ass fight.
Might wanna find your
place in all of it.
[ISHIDA grunting]
Am I to understand
that you forgave him?
Forgave him?
Heh.
[DATE] You know I'm
not that admirable.
But I have seen that look
in his eyes before.
Many times.
Often in a mirror, no doubt.
[DATE] You don't always gotta
die to end up Hell.
Crawlin' up outta there alive
has a lot to do with luck.
So, yeah, maybe.
Lord Masamune?
Let's just say I'm a lucky guy.
[ISHIDA grunts]
Sanada.
Tell me something.
Regarding Mitsunari.
Does he still despise me?
[SANADA] Master Ishida is
a man with a pure heart.
[TOKUGAWA] Yes, and he is
easily hurt because of it.
To understand each another
we msut face each other.
That's what you said, wasn't it?
[TOKUGAWA] What lies stretched
across this world is strength.
Yes, Lord Hideyoshi,
you were right.
People want to be enveloped
in great strength
to gain a sense of security.
I, too, sought strength,
and many of those who placed
their faith in me in the past,
I sent to their deaths.
But still, that cannot be!
If we accept such
a world as normal,
people will die all too easily!
That is why I have
decided to take
all the strength in this world
and conceal it in the cloak
of our shared bonds.
[TOKUGAWA]
From this day forth,
I will be guilty of the heinous
crime of deceiving the country!
[OTANI groaning]
For... Mitsunari, I...
[OTANI]
Mitsunari, go on.
Go... see... that.. man.
[NARRATOR]
Next time: "Guide."