[SOLDIERS yell]
[DATE]
I came all this way
for a good fight against
someone worthy of facing me.
And no demon resurrection's
gonna stop me!
[DATE]
Right?
Sanada Yukimura?
[SANADA] Lord Masamune,
I look forward to facing you
in combat once again!
A fire burns in my soul
for a true challenge!
This party's about
to turn rough.
Let's get ready to rumble! Yeah!
[DATE] Kojuro.
What the hell's that crap?
Honnoji Temple, my lord.
But it burned to the ground
along with Oda Nobunaga.
It was reduced to
ashes before my eyes.
Its mere existence is beyond the
realm of human comprehension.
[DATE]
Cool.
Then we should go investigate.
The One-Eyed Dragon ain't
afraid of no ghosts!
You have my back!
[KATAKURA]
Sir!
[SANADA] What the devil is going
on with that dark cloud?
No matter.
Whatever's behind
this disturbance,
I pledge to put a stop to it.
So that the battle between
Ishida and Tokugawa
can continue!
[SANADA yells]
The audacity.
Swine.
You will pay!
So, you've come to
resurrect your master.
Mitsuhide.
[KOBAYAKAWA]
Whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa.
What's going on?!
Lord Kingo, please!
You've got to do something!
[whimpers] I don't know how!
Forgive me!
Mr. Tenkai!
Mr, Tenkai! [laughs]
Uh!
[gasps]
No, please! I don't wanna die!
[KOBAYAKAWA]
Thank you Tenkai!
[KOBAYAKAWA whimpers]
[TENKAI] This one is
to be left unspoiled.
Are you able to control
those things, Mr. Tenkai?
[TENKAI]
Kingo.
You should leave this place.
Go back to your home.
But what's gonna happen to you?
[TENKAI]
You must go!
[KOBAYAKAWA whimpers]
Venerable Tenkai!
I'll be waiting!
I'll keep waiting for you!
[TENKAI]
Sleep for now, dear lady.
Embraced within
this dark cocoon.
[TENKAI]
Lord Nobunaga.
I eagerly await your
glorious return.
I kill one, two take it's place!
[MATSU]
Keiji!
Your griping about it isn't
going to change anything!
[SARUTOBI] Hey, mighty
mercenaries of Saika!
Can't you guys do something
about these creeps?
[SAIKA]
You must be joking!
Dead warriors coming
back to life.
There aren't enough bullets
in the world for that!
That said, we're
low on ammunition.
Of course.
[POSSESSED SOLDIER N groans]
I'll protect you!
I won't live my life regretting
the times I did nothing!
[yells]
Maeda.
The Saika folk honor the
nobility you have shown.
The time has come to
launch our attack!
Are you ready, men?
I think I've heard this horse's
rampaging hoofbeats before.
[POSSESSED SOLDIERS groan]
[DATE yells]
[SARUTOBI]
I knew it!
Here comes the One-Eyed Dragon!
[POSSESSED SOLDIERS groaning]
[SANADA yells]
[SARUTOBI]
There's the Commander, too.
[SANADA]
Sasuke, are you unhurt?
[DATE]
Hey, Takeda ninja.
We're here for the same thing.
To send all these party
crashers back to hell!
[SARUTOBI]
Very well then, One-Eyed Dragon.
Commander.
A word of advice, if I may.
The best way to accomplish that
is to let these people
through to the Temple.
[DATE]
Magoichi?
[SANADA]
Let Lady Saika?
He's right.
Huh.
[SANADA]
Very well then.
We can keep them
occupied out here.
Now go.
Great!
Sounds like one helluva warm up.
You go have fun with your
unfinished business.
I thank you.
Just leave the vanguard to me.
[SAIKA]
Assault formation!
We take the Temple!
[SAIKA FOLK yell]
Sarutobi.
You're certainly coming
up in the world.
You just told Lord
Masamune what to do.
[SARUTOBI gasps]
Wow.
You sound like such a square!
Now, instead of
focusing on that.
Look.
Uh?
[SARUTOBI]
If I didn't know any better,
I'd say they were havin' fun!
[CHOSOKABE]
Tis an ill wind.
Strange happenin's are
taking place all around.
[CHOSOKABE gasps]
[MORI] Letting your attention
stray in the midst of battle.
It would seem you
are as inattentive
to your surroundings as ever,
Chosokabe.
[CHOSOKABE]
And what about you?
Always peerin' down your
nose at everybody!
I look forward to knockin'
you off your perch!
You're wasting your time.
I already know exactly
how this battle will end.
And you have no
hope for victory.
[TENKAI] You took your
time getting here.
And you're too late.
With the use of
Lady O-Ichi's life,
The Devil King of the Sixth
Heaven shall be resurrected.
You mean...?!
[TENKAI]
Come!
Through the maelstrom of chaos.
We will start over
from the beginning.
Racing across the
same battlefields
we conquered once before.
That intoxicating excitement
within the flames.
[laughs]
[groans]
[TENKAI]
Lord... Nobunaga.
The way you look.
Why?
Does this mean I
have failed you?
Hear me.
I am the new Devil King.
O-Ichi.
[TENKAI]
No! This... this can't be.
I planned it.
It was perfect.
[TENKAI groans]
[KEIJI gasps]
No! Lady O-Ichi!
Formation.
Take aim!
[KEIJI]
Hold on!
You can't shoot at Lady O-Ichi!
[SAIKA]
That is the Devil King!
An amalgamation of
misfortune and terror.
Something not human.
Now step aside!
You can't!
Keiji!
Fire!
[laughs]
[SAIKA grunts]
Load the next round, quickly!
Fire every last bullet
we brought with us!
Captain!
We're completely
out of ammunition!
[SAIKA grunts]
It's all I've got left.
Stop, O-Ichi.
Get a hold of yourself!
[ICHI]
Hm...
[MATSU]
Don't let him control you.
Just snap out of it!
Hey! Keep out of the way!
You could get hurt!
[MATSU]
I will do no such thing!
I am a warrior's wife!
I'm quite capable of
taking care of myself.
O-Ichi.
If you let this continue,
you will end up
losing everything!
But, I...
This world has
nothing left for me.
Remember!
That man who loved you dearly!
Those days of youthful bliss!
[gasps]
[gasping]
[MATSU]
I know you haven't forgotten.
Those feelings.
Why you fell in love with him.
The way you'd ride together
across the fields.
You looked so happy.
You and Lord Nagamasa.
[ICHI]
Uh!
Dearest Nagamasa.
Are you ready to let him go?
To lose your memories
of your late husband?!
No!
[KEIJI yells]
[KEIJI]
Now! Shoot, Magoichi!
Keiji!
Maeda!
[KEIJI grunting]
[SAIKA growls]
Don't worry about it!
A real man'll put his life at
risk for the woman he loves!
Keiji.
[groans]
[ICHI gasps]
[MATSU]
Lady O-Ichi!
[SAIKA]
Keiji!
Hey!
Hang in there!
[POSSESSED SOLDIERS moan]
[DATE]
Huh?
[SANADA]
Strange.
[gasps]
[SARUTOBI]
Kasuga.
About time.
I promised to rescue you,
never specified when.
Enjoy this while you can.
I only sleep in the
arms of Lord Kenshin.
[SARUTOBI]
Hmph.
Maeda.
Time to go.
[KEIJI]
Let me lie here a little longer.
I had faith that a dead-eye
like you would avoid
hitting anything vital.
But what really surprised me
was when you called me Keiji,
instead of Maeda.
Come on.
Say my name one more time.
Shut your mouth.
It looks like Lady O-Ichi
is going to be all right.
Brave men of Saika,
our mission's complete!
Our force will now
move to disengage!
Let's head home on the double!
[SAIKA FOLK cheer]
[DATE] Everything that stood
in our way's gone now.
We're back to bein'
enemies again.
[SANADA] I've not forgotten
that promise you made
at the tea house.
I eagerly await the chance
to face you in combat.
Of course.
But before I square
off against you,
I gotta win my honor
back from your boss.
You are the summit I
aspire to conquer one day.
Such is the magnitude
of my unwavering will!
Ha! Sanada Yukimura!
I look forward to our fight.
And I won't lose
sight of it again.
Let's meet back here, once
I'm someone I can be proud of!
I'll be here waiting for you!
Nice!
[KURODA]
Bam!
[KURODA grunts]
At last, I've finally found you!
Fuma!
Stop right there!
I can't let the two of
you fight because of me!
[KURODA]
What's that?
I'm just trying to get free.
But I'm flattered.
[TSURUHIME]
No, it's just that...
Kuroda.
That is... Uh.
[KURODA]
Huh?
I'm really sorry!
My divination was all mixed up.
Cause...
There was something else
that made me misread it.
[squeals]
Wait. So this guy
doesn't have the key?
I'm afraid not.
Uh! It's right up there!
Huh?
[KURODA]
On the bird?!
This is ridiculous!
How can anybody have a
string of luck this rotten?
Huh?
Well, things look like
they might just work out!
Yo're out of luck key-crow!
I'm comin' to get ya!
[KURODA]
Up up and away!
Happy trails, guy!
Now we're alone,
just the two of us.
[squeals]
I feel so nervous.
You're so dreamy!
[squeals, grunts]
Gloaming feathers! Wait for me!
[OTANI] The line has been drawn,
and I shall let no one pass.
To inflict further suffering
upon Mitsunari,
I will not stand for it!
Heh. What a beautiful
friendship you must have!
[OTANI] Men like you
would never understand.
[KATAKURA] Lord Masamune, please
make haste to where Ishida is.
It would be my privilege to
fight this man for you.
Kojuro.
Don't forget to have fun.
[OTANI]
Come back!
[KATAKURA yells]
You'll want to keep
your focus on me.
[OTANI growls]
[SANADA]
Lord Tokugawa.
[TOKUGAWA] I'm glad to
see you've stepped up.
Not as another warrior, but as
the commander of the Takeda.
Sanada.
This is truly as you
were meant to be.
I have kept you
waiting a long time.
They'll speak of this day,
the fight to determine
the Tiger's successor.
But I believe that
it will amount
to something even greater.
I, Sanada Yukimura,
challenge you to a fair fight!
Bear witness to the ferocity
of my crimson soul!
I gave my word that I
would fight Mitsunari here.
I accept your challenge!
Come, Voracious Tiger of Takeda!
[SANADA yells]
[TOKUGAWA yells]
[SANADA yelling]
[TOKUGAWA yelling]
[BOTH grunt]
[SOLDIERS yelling]
[BOTH yell]
[BOTH grunt]
[OTANI]
Hm? What is that?
[KATAKURA] Looks like
Sanada and Tokugawa
are locked in a battle
for supremacy.
[OTANI]
Your commander is under attack.
How can you be so calm?
Unlike your forces, we're
all equals in the east.
Besides my only commander
is Lord Date Masamune.
[OTANI]
Mm...
And at this moment,
I'm not interested in anything
except taking you down!
[KASUGA]
Isn't that...?
[SARUTOBI]
Yeah.
Guess it's begun.
Don't you need to go help him?
The commander has grown.
He doesn't need any
more help from me.
[SHIMAZU grunts]
[SHIMAZU] Ya got no time for
distractions, Master Tadakatsu!
I sense it!
The energy of the
Tiger within you!
I can detect the vital energy
of your Tiger as well,
Master Tokugawa!
[BOTH grunt]
It's strong.
You must've struggled and fought
hard to face your demons!
I wrestled with it.
We both revere Shingen
as our mentor and yet,
it makes no sense.
How could you and I
end up so different?!
Did you realize why that was?
[SANADA] All I was doing
was walking behind my lord,
in his shadow.
But you...
Your perception was
keener that mine.
You were able to recognize
the true nature
of His Lordship's spirit.
Yes.
Lord Shingen has the
strength of bonds.
He's honest.
And his spirit has won
the hearts of many,
forging bonds with them all.
With you and I, and
every citizen of Kai.
I'll go even further!
I hope to forge bonds
with all the people
of our tumultuous land!
Really?
All of them?
I think you're mistaken.
[gasps]
[SANADA]
His Lordship has crossed swords
with Lord Uesugi
times beyond counting
and a bond was forged
between them.
Strengthening with every clash.
But what you are doing...
It looks to me as though you
are severing those bonds!
[gasps]
[SANADA]
What I have set my gaze upon,
that is the real
heart of the Tiger,
which turns his
eyes upon himself.
As the elder Tiger's disciple,
I will now reveal
this truth to you!
[SANADA yelling]
[TOKUGAWA yells]
[TOKUGAWA gasps]
[gasps]
What will you do, Tiger?
[SANADA growls]
[gasps]
[SANADA yells]
Wha...?
[TOKUGAWA chuckles]
Shared bonds and heart.
Real strength.
Lord Shingen's spirit
is truly vast.
Beyond vast.
And it is my duty to
safeguard this spirit
I have inherited
from His Lordship.
[TOKUGAWA]
True.
[SANADA] Though I may be granted
half the land of the rising sun,
my desire will never change.
This is the truth of my soul
that will forever echo
throughout the heavens.
You are the Tiger's
rightful heir.
Without doubt.
[SANADA gasping]
[TOKUGAWA]
Sanada?
[SANADA gasping]
Don't strain yourself!
[SANADA groans]
I'll keep getting
up, no matter what!
My soul burns with desire.
The feelings in my heart urge
me to fulfill the promise
I made to Lord Masamune!
You, too, must face
the true feelings
taking root in your heart.
My heartfelt desire?
[TOKUGAWA]
My promise.
[footsteps]
Not you again.
[DATE] Time to settle the
score from the day we met.
It won't be pretty!
[NARRATOR]
Next time: "Verdict."