[NARRATOR]
The Sengoku Period,
a time of chaos and bloodshed.
[SOLDIERS shouting]
[NARRATOR] In this
period of warring states,
dozens of feudal lords
vied for supremacy,
hoping to unite this
land of the rising sun.
[NARRATOR]
Among them, Oda Nobunaga,
who had nearly brought the
entire country under his rule.
[NARRATOR]
But at Honnoji Temple,
he was betrayed and laid low
by his retainer,
Akechi Mitsuhide.
However, Akechi himself was
laid low by Toyotomi Hideyoshi.
And the world was once again
plunged into the
maelstrom of war.
Recruiting one
warlord after another,
Toyotomi quickly became
a force to be reckoned with.
Many a feudal lord
fell before his might,
and the number who openly
defied him grew thin.
The Toyotomi Army was now
on the verge of engulfing
even Hojo in the east.
As if to rise in rebellion
against Toyotomi,
one man rode in haste to Hojo
Ujimasa's Odawara Castle.
The so-called "Big Boss"
of Oshu, Date Masamune.
[DATE]
Are you ready, guys?
[DATE ARMY]
Yeah!
[DATE scoffs]
Let's get this
conquest party started!
[SANADA]
Your Lordship!
The Toyotomi, sir!
They were seen at Odawara!
If they have already
invaded the Hojo,
our Takeda army must
respond swiftly--
[TAKEDA]
Yukimura, you are too anxious!
[SANADA grunting]
[SARUTOBI sighs]
[grunts]
Lordship!
Should Odawara fall,
it is inevitable they will
next invade Kai itself!
[TAKEDA]
All the more reason, boy!
[grunts]
[TAKEDA]
In times such as this,
the duty of an army's general is
to calmly discern the situation.
[gasps]
[SANADA] Your Lordship,
you are truly great.
I sought to launch us headlong
with only shallow thoughts and
no concern for what lies ahead.
[TAKEDA]
Buffoon!
[SANADA grunting]
And yet, should you
lose that fire,
you would be a warrior no more.
[SANADA]
Your Lordship!
The fire in my heart. Grr.
Burns bright!
Become an inferno, Yukimura!
Your Lordship!
[SANADA]
My fire shall not extinguish!
[TAKEDA] Yes! More!
Burn more, Yukimura!
--[SANADA] Your Lordship!
--[TAKEDA] Yukimura!
[SANADA]
Your Lordship!
--[TAKEDA] Yukimura!
--I missed this.
[SANADA]
Your Lordship!
[HOJO]
Curses!
Damn that upstart Toyotomi!
How can he "rule the
world with strength"
with neither pride nor dignity?
Hideyoshi.
It seems your personal
involvement won't be needed.
[coughs]
[TOYOTOMI]
Hanbei.
It is your resourcefulness that
has gotten my army this far.
Take the rest that
you have earned.
Thank you, Hideyoshi.
I will do just that.
Dear Mitsunari and Ieyasu,
I leave the rest in your hands.
[TOKUGAWA]
Right.
[ISHIDA]
I, Mitsunari.
Along with Ieyasu,
swear upon my life,
that I shall be of service to
the cause, without fail.
[coughs]
Fall, Hojo. This country no
longer has use for the weak.
[HOJO] O, great ancestors!
Tell me what I should--
No! I have decided!
[HOJO SOLDIER 1A]
Please my lord! Don't do this!
[HOJO]
You will unhand me!
Just once! I, too,
would taste victor--!
--[cracking]
--[HOJO] ...ry...
Oh! My back!
[HOJO SOLDIER 1A]
My lord!
[HOJO]
Where is Fuma? What of Fuma?!
[HOJO ARMY grunting]
[SAIKA]
Ringing to the heavens!
Flashing on earth!
Tremble before our
mighty onslaught!
Fire!
[gunshots]
[NINJA 1A groans]
[SAIKA] The weapons of the
Saika will change war itself.
Do you feel it?
Mere ninja are of
no consequence.
For we are the proud folk
of the Saika Faction!
[distant gunshots]
[TAKENAKA]
It appears the Saika Faction
are doing good work
at the west gate.
As long as nothing
unsavory happens,
Odawara Castle is ours.
[coughs]
Alas, Hideyoshi.
It seems fate will not allow
me to walk by your side.
[KATAKURA]
Lord Masamune!
If you rush in, it will
throw the column--
[DATE]
No problem!
There's no one down this
road who can stop me!
Until I take Odawara--
No, take the whole country,
I got no plans on slowin' down!
[DATE]
Sanada Yukimura.
I'm already one
step ahead of you.
What are you doing
to take this country?
[TAKEDA SOLDIER 1A]
My lord!
What is your report?
[TAKEDA SOLDIER A]
A lookout near Odawara
reports an army
quickly advancing.
From what land does it hail?
[TAKEDA SOLDIER A]
Sir.
It is my understanding the
army comes from Oshu.
Lord Masamune?
[TAKEDA] Ah, so the One-Eyed
Dragon makes his move.
--Your Lordsh--
--[TAKEDA] Silence, Yukimura!
But Lordship, I have
yet to say anything.
[TAKEDA]
I know what you wish to say.
You would call upon
Takeda to follow Date.
Rise up in arms to
vanquish the Toyotomi.
That is indeed what I would
wish! And then I will battle
Lord Masamune for
control of the country.
--This time I--
--[TAKEDA] You Buffoon!
[SANADA grunts]
[TAKEDA]
Now is not yet the time to act.
Be that as it may,
if Odawara falls.
[TAKEDA] The Hojo will
not fall so easily.
[SANADA]
But as the Toyotomi stand now,
Lord Hojo is not
capable of repell--
You still don't see, Yukimura.
Toyotomi's enemy is
neither Hojo, nor Date.
[SANADA gasps]
Then, Which army could it be?
[TAKEDA]
There is one more Tiger.
[gasps]
Tiger?
How goes it, Sakai?
We're calling on the
Hojo side to surrender.
But they don't seem
ready to trust us yet.
Then, we wait.
The fact that they
have not attacked
is evidence of their hesitation.
With the west gate having
been breached by Saika,
Hojo's men must know
there is no need
to guard the east gate here.
I would like to avoid
any pointless bloodshed.
[SAKAI]
Agreed.
--[gate rattles]
--[TOKUGAWA ARMY gasps]
--[SAKAI] Ah!
--[TOKUGAWA ARMY sighs]
I am glad you've
made this decision.
[HOJO SOLDIER 1D] We are here to
seek protection, as promised.
Of course, men!
--You will be treated with-
--[gunshot]
[gasps]
[groans]
[HOJO ARMY gasps]
[HOJO ARMY grunting]
What is the meaning of this?!
Enough!
[HOJO ARMY grunting]
You... cowardly...
[TOYOTOMI ARMY yells]
Toyotomi's men?
[OTANI]
What a glorious feat, Tokugawa.
[OTANI giggles]
Gyobu! Explain this!
[OTANI] Have you forgotten
the Taiko's order?
Every last Hojo soldier
is to be killed.
But, Gyobu.
[OTANI] Thanks to you,
I coaxed open the east gate
suffering not a single casualty.
[TOYOTOMI ARMY yelling]
[OTANI] The main keep should
fall in short order.
--[OTANI giggles]
--[TOKUGAWA growls]
[ISHIDA] It seems Gyobu has
now breached the east gate.
[TOYOTOMI]
Hm.
[TOYOTOMI SOLDIER 1A]
News, my lord!
--Yes, what is it?
--An army rapidly approaches
from north of Odawara!
The banner is that
of the Date of Oshu!
The One-Eyed Dragon.
What does he hope to gain
with just a single army?
[ISHIDA]
Lord Hideyoshi,
this rebel wishes
the Toyotomi harm.
I seek permission to
put him to the sword.
[TOYOTOMI]
Hm. And I grant it.
[ISHIDA]
My lord.
For your trust. I am grateful.
[KASUGA] I assume you think
you're being stealthy?
[SARUTOBI] Well I wasn't
trying to hide, per se,
but you took forever
to notice me.
[KASUGA] The Uesugi and the
Takeda may have common ground,
but I have no interest
in making friends.
How 'bout more than friends?
So, how's the battle
down there going?
[KASUGA] Do you not know?
Toyotomi won.
Really. You think so?
You're saying the
Hojo could win?
[SARUTOBI]
Well I wouldn't go that far.
Funny thing about war, though:
y'never know what might happen.
[DATE]
Straight on!
We do this in one fell swoop!
[KATAKURA grunts]
[DATE]
What's wrong, Kojuro?
That's not the face of a guy
about to hit the party scene.
The Toyotomi have
most likely become
aware of our movements.
An ambush could be lying in wait
for us at nearly any turn.
[DATE] Hideyoshi'd never
pull such a petty stunt.
And if he does,
it just saves me from havin'
to hunt the monkey down!
[KATAKURA] My lord, do not
underestimate Toyotomi!
Please.
[KATAKURA] The military might
he's exerted in the west
is a very real threat--
Your job is to guard my back.
Long as I've got you
watchin' my blind side,
there's no way I'll ever fall!
Toyotomi ain't nothin'
but the first step
on a longer journey.
Follow me there, Kojuro!
Sir!
[ISHIDA]
Lord Hideyoshi!
He is the key!
Lord Hideyoshi
will rule supreme,
Lord Hanbei will
oversee the world,
Gyobu will control the people,
Ieyasu will direct the troops,
and I, will continue to serve.
And any who dare to stand in
our way... Shall regret it!
[TOYOTOMI]
What do you want, Ieyasu?
[DATE]
Whoa!
Who the hell is that?
Sir, that's...
[KATAKURA] Toyotomi Hideyoshi's
trusted enforcer,
Ishida Mitsunari.
[DATE] So they think an errand
boy's enough to stop me, huh?
Jeez, they'll gimme a complex.
All right.
Here's your one chance
to take my head.
But if you blow it,
You are gonna be sorry. You see?
[TOKUGAWA]
Lord Hideyoshi.
I beseech you,
withdraw your army.
This is the wrong path.
[TOYOTOMI]
It is that spirit
that made this
whole country weak.
[TOKUGAWA] You have changed,
Lord Hideyoshi.
I fear the illness that
eats away at Lord Hanbei
now taints your heart as well.
[TOYOTOMI]
Ludicrous.
Is there no way
you will listen?
[TOYOTOMI] If I say no,
what will you do?
Will you show me my end?
Let's say you do.
With what will you
rule this country?
[TOKUGAWA]
Common bonds.
[TOYOTOMI]
What?
[TOKUGAWA]
I believe the bonds we share
hold the greatest power.
That is how I will
rule this land.
Through the strength of
that which unites us!
[TOYOTOMI]
Strength? You are weak, Ieyasu.
Lord Hideyoshi. Your end is now!
Ready when you are.
Come at me, bro!
[grunts]
[laughs]
I have no words
for a mere rebel!
Blast!
[TOKUGAWA grunts]
[ISHIDA, KATAKURA grunting]
Kojuro!
[TOKUGAWA, TOYOTOMI grunting]
[KATAKURA, ISHIDA grunting]
Now die.
[DATE]
Wait!
[BOTH grunt]
Lord Masamune,
you mustn't--
So unlike you, Kojuro.
This guy's just a warm-up!
[ISHIDA grunts]
Date Masamune, Big Boss
of Oshu, full speed ah--
Your name is meaningless!
Now quietly be sliced to pieces!
[BOTH grunting]
As proof of the devotion,
I most reverently offer
to Lord Hideyoshi.
Ha! That big monkey?
Y'can't think the
guy's all that!
Silence, bastard!
[TOYOTOMI, TOKUGAWA grunting]
[ISHIDA] The Toyotomi stand
at the very pinnacle!
All who stand against
Lord Hideyoshi...
[DATE grunting]
...Will become naught
but corpses!
In the gleaming brilliance
that is Lord Hideyoshi,
your foul existence...
[yells]
[ISHIDA]
...has no place!
[DATE shouts]
Shit!
[TOYOTOMI, TOKUGAWA grunting]
[DATE]
Death Fang!
[groans]
[ISHIDA]
Your efforts are pointless.
The moment you lifted your
blade against Lord Hideyoshi,
your fate was sealed!
[ISHIDA] Trampled like a weed
on the path to military rule!
[yells]
[KATAKURA]
I won't allow it!
[grunting]
[DATE]
Koju... ro!
[grunts]
Lord Hideyoshi,
please grant Ieyasu and I
permission to present you
with this glorious victory.
[TOYOTOMI]
Hmm?
[yelling]
[yelling continues]
[gasps]
Hideyoshi!
[TOYOTOMI yells]
That is... Lord Hideyoshi!
[ISHIDA grunts]
[DATE groans]
Lord Hideyoshi!
What has happened?
Is that?
That was?
Is it over?
[ISHIDA]
Lord Hideyoshi!
Someone answer me!
[gasps]
[ISHIDA]
Lord Hanbei.
Lord Hanbei!
[grunts]
What happened here?
[TAKENAKA]
My dear Mitsunari.
Will you be all right?
[TAKENAKA]
Never mind me.
Hideyoshi's the only concern.
I've placed this burden on you.
I am sorry, my dear Mitsunari.
I will be right back.
Hideyoshi. Take care of him.
[TOYOTOMI SOLDIER 1B]
Master Mitsunari!
[ISHIDA]
What is it?
Has a Hojo spy infiltrated us?
[TOYOTOMI SOLDIER 1B]
It was Tokugawa.
Tokugawa Ieyasu
has turned traitor!
[TOYOTOMI SOLDIER 1B shouts]
Ieyasu is not that kind of man.
[gasps]
Hideyoshi.
Hideyoshi!
[ISHIDA]
Lord Hideyoshi!
Hideyoshi!
Please answer me, my lord!
Lord Hideyoshi!
Ieyasu, tell me
how this happened!
Were you not standing
at our lord's side?
Why did you not protect him?
[TOKUGAWA]
He left me no choice.
[ISHIDA gasps]
What... are you saying?
[TOKUGAWA]
This world will find peace
through the bonds we all share.
Not by force.
What are you saying?
[ISHIDA]
No...
You... Traitor!
You betrayed us?
Ieyasu?
[ISHIDA growls]
He trusted you!
We all did.
And... And you killed him!
Damn it.
Hideyoshi and Hanbei had a plan.
Did you not share their
dream for this world?
No.
That dream belongs in the past.
[gasps]
This is goodbye.
Wait. Ieyasu.
Listen to me!
[ISHIDA grunts]
Ieyasu!
[yells]
[ISHIDA]
Lord Hideyoshi!
[ISHIDA grunts]
Lord Hanbei.
[TAKENAKA]
Mitsunari, dear boy.
[ISHIDA]
I'm so sorry.
Lord Hideyoshi is.
Ah. Hideyoshi, you have
finally returned.
[gasps]
[TAKENAKA]
I'm feeling much better now.
So I'll be able to join
you in our next battle.
With our dear boys
Ieyasu and Mitsunari,
the Toyotomi are strong.
[ISHIDA]
Lord... Hanbei.
[TAKENAKA] What we've dreamed
of, is almost within reach.
Come, Hideyoshi.
Whom shall we... conquer next?
[ISHIDA]
Lord Hanbei?
Lord Hanbei!
Lord Hanb--
[grunting]
[yells]
[ISHIDA]
Lord Hanbei!
[OTANI] So. Tokugawa turned
everything upside down.
Ieyasu.
Ieyasu! Ieyasu!
I swear this,
upon my life.
You shall not...
get away with this!
I... will... kill you!
[ISHIDA screams]
[OTANI]
The misery.
It rains down from the heavens.
[ISHIDA]
Ieyasu!
[ISHIDA yelling]
[NARRATOR]
Odawara, devastated.
Toyotomi Hideyoshi, dead.
It was a turning point.
And the land of the rising sun
would grow ever more turbulent.
[ALL gasp]
[NARRATOR] With all
roads, leading to Sekigahara.
[NARRATOR]
Next time, "Chaos."