[NARRATOR]
The Sengoku Period,
a time of chaos and bloodshed.
Oda Nobunaga had nearly brought
the entire country
under his rule.
But at Honnoji, he was betrayed
and laid low by his retainer,
Akechi Mitsuhide.
After that,
Toyotomi Hideyoshi struck east,
and subdued much of the land.
Before falling by the hand of
his retainer, Tokugawa Ieyasu.
Lord Hideyoshi. Your end is now!
I swear this, upon my life.
I... will... kill you!
[DATE]
Hats off to ya, kid.
Ya really put me in
the ass-kickin' mood!
[yells]
[DATE]
Magnum Step!
[SANADA]
Raging Flames!
Lord Masamune.
Yours is the strength
that quickens my pulse!
[clattering]
[KATAKURA grunts]
[DATE SOLDIER 2A]
Ambush!
[DATE SOLDIERS shouting]
[KATAKURA]
Remain in formation, men!
We'll break through
their right flank!
[SANADA]
Your Lordship!
I come to you bearing urgent
news from the battlefield!
Sasuke reports--!
[TAKEDA]
That is enough!
[SANADA grunting]
[TAKEDA]
Have you no patience?
[SANADA]
But, Your Lordship!
Sasuke reports that
Toyotomi Hideyoshi
has met his end at Odawara!
I am well aware.
[gasps]
[TAKEDA] An old friend
brought word of his death.
[SANADA]
An old, friend?
[SHIMAZU]
Shimazu Yoshihiro, of Satsuma.
Shingen an' me raised
a fair bit o' hell,
back when we was yer age.
Lord Shimazu, I most earnestly
beg your forgiveness--!
[SHIMAZU] You must be that
young cub he goes on about.
Full o' piss
and vinegar! Ha, ha!
[SANADA]
Yes, sir. Many thanks!
I'll take my leave now!
Yer a lucky bastard,
y'know that?
Having a young'un
to leave it all to.
Too many lessons have
yet gone untaught.
[groans]
[SANADA] Sasuke! Our lord
is with a friend of old!
How could you let me barge in?
[SARUTOBI]
My bad.
Hey! Next time,
I'll be sure to tie you up
before I give you
important news.
Of all men, Tokugawa Ieyasu,
turned traitor.
You say it like it's a shock.
But maybe this is the
guy he's always been.
[ISHIDA]
He trusted you, Ieyasu!
[ISHIDA] And you struck,
like a thief in the night.
[grunting]
[ISHIDA]
Please. Lord Hideyoshi.
Lord Hanbei.
Grant me but one word
of comfort from beyond.
Allow me to join you.
[OTANI] Mitsunari, you are now
the master of this castle.
You are much mistaken, Gyobu.
Only Lord Hideyoshi could
lay claim to this castle,
this clan, this country!
[ISHIDA sobs]
[OTANI] Then this is
the darkest of days.
With none to champion
Hideyoshi's memory,
Tokugawa will conquer all.
[ISHIDA]
Tokugawa will what?
[OTANI] Not only did he
take the Taiko's life,
he means to bend
the Taiko's exploits
to his own duplicitous ends.
What? Damn him.
[ISHIDA]
Ieyasu!
You are a villain and
you will die like one!
[OTANI giggles] Even now,
Ieyasu grows more powerful.
Absorbing the broken Hojo,
and speaking mild words of
friendship all the while.
[ISHIDA]
He, a man who slew his master,
dares to adopt the
guise of peace?
[growls]
[ISHIDA]
Victory is ours.
[TOKUGAWA] You wage war
like a man possessed.
[chuckles]
[TOKUGAWA] Fighting with
such unchecked zeal
is a good way to end
up dead, my friend.
[ISHIDA]
I care nothing for my own skin.
I believe in Lord Hideyoshi's
grand conquest. Do you not?
[TOKUGAWA] I believe in the
unified nation he pursues.
And...
[ISHIDA]
Damn you!
In the friendship I
have forged with him.
[ISHIDA]
You liar!
I'll cut that false
tongue out of your head!
[panting]
[ISHIDA]
Toyotomi's noble blood.
It is on my hands.
Why did I fall for
Ieyasu's honeyed words?
Lord Hideyoshi.
Lord Hanbei.
Know that, if only
I had the power,
I would kill even the
memory of that dark day!
[OTANI]
Mitsunari.
The Taiko's betrayal and death
murdered you in all
ways but the flesh.
To think, that further
suffering may await you.
I deem it, a grave injustice.
[ISHIDA]
Lord Hideyoshi.
[TOKUGAWA]
Lord Shingen. I have come.
As a young man,
you defeated me on this field.
Taught me a great deal.
Time to show you how much.
[SAKAI] Fitting that fate
has brought you back here
to Mikata-gahara,
where you weathered such loss.
I always knew this
day would come.
[TOKUGAWA] Remember, our goal
isn't to crush the Takeda.
If we do this right, I think we
can convince them to join us.
Lord Shingen, today I will
teach you of something!
The strength of the bonds
that I have forged!
[shouts]
Looks like he's here.
[TAKEDA SOLDIER 2A]
Commander.
Word comes that
Tokugawa Ieyasu's
forces have invaded our
land at Mikata-gahara!
[SANADA]
They what?
Your Lordship!
There is no time to waste.
Impossible!
[TAKEDA]
Ieyasu awaits us.
[SANADA] Yes, but,
the messenger only just arrived!
Upon the wind. I smell
the soul of a rival tiger.
[KATAKURA]
They dog our every step.
And this terrain grows
less familiar by the hour.
Wha-? Another ambush, sir?
Hardly. Would that it were.
Our pursuers have
harried us into lands
belonging to the
War God of Echigo himself.
Uesugi will brook no trespass.
[UESUGI] You have entered
my hallowed abode.
But I fear you will find no
succor here, defeated dragon.
[grunts]
[TAKEDA] Quite a sight.
His army cuts a fine figure.
Glad I came to visit
when I did, Shingen.
This young buck done laid
out a banquet for me!
Happy huntin', yeah?
[TAKEDA]
We'll meet again someday.
Till then.
[TAKEDA grunting]
[grunts]
War God of Echigo!
We intrude upon your
land in extremis!
We were driven here
at the barrel of a gun!
I beg of you!
Forgive this act we
had no mind to commit!
Forgiveness?
You ask for the one scruple none
can afford in these bloody days.
Are you a holy man or
a warrior, Katakura?
Ha. You were right
to shame me thus.
To think that the
Right Eye of the Dragon,
would sully his
master with such talk!
All I want, is to wash away
this stain with death!
[UESUGI] And that would
atone for your cowardice?
[KATAKURA]
No, of course not.
Only valor in battle
can right that wrong!
That's why, Uesugi Kenshin,
to preserve my men,
I will beat you!
[SOLDIERS yelling]
Sanada Genjiro Yukimura
defends these lands!
[grunting]
Master.
Would it kill you to
give me a heads-up
before you go charging in?
[grunting]
It would seem that
the Tokugawa soldiers
are as fierce as their lord.
[SARUTOBI]
Fair enough.
Kinda makes me wonder, though.
How come our men
aren't stepping up?
[whistling]
[SARUTOBI]
What the?
Yellow flares herald
an emergency!
[yells]
[grunts]
Sasuke! Fight on without me!
I shall return!
[TOKUGAWA SOLDIERS gasp]
[grunts]
[KATAKURA grunts]
He stands as though at ease,
but every fiber of his
being is poised to strike.
I have but once chance.
[KATAKURA]
Princess Kaguya!
Coveted by many.
Caught by none!
[KATAKURA grunts]
[gasps]
It seems the Right Eye of
the Dragon has blinked.
[KATAKURA]
What?
[KATAKURA groans]
[SOLDIERS yelling]
[SANADA]
Your Lordship!
I came as quickly as I could!
[gasps]
[SANADA]
Your Lordship!
[grunting]
Your moniker is an
apt one, War God.
Before you end my life,
grant me this boon.
If I, Katakura Kojuro,
might buy the Date Army's
freedom by the loss of my head,
then take it!
[gasps]
[UESUGI] Death is a
solace you do not deserve.
In this moment,
you are neither retainer,
nor general, nor man.
All I see here are
soldiers without a leader.
There is no honor
in fighting you.
[gasps]
[SOLDIERS shouting]
[SARUTOBI]
C'mon, men! Hang in there!
You don't want Master Sanada
to have all the fun!
Oh, great!
[SARUTOBI]
Look who brought his giant!
[shouts]
[gasps] All is fair in
love and war, but still!
[SHIMAZU]
I'll open up that lobster!
[SARUTOBI]
Lord Shimazu!
This is not your fight!
[SHIMAZU] That don't make
no never-mind to me!
[SOLDIERS shouting]
[SHIMAZU]
Put up your dukes, boy!
[grunting]
Why hasn't he made it back yet?
[SANADA gasps, sobs]
[SANADA]
Please, Your Lordship.
You can't leave us!
[grunts]
[gasps]
[TAKEDA]
Yukimura!
[SANADA gasps]
What ails you, my lord?
Whatever it could be.
I'll bring you the cure!
Silence!
[TAKEDA groans]
[SANADA]
I have you, my lord.
Yukimura.
[SANADA gasps]
I'm right here, my lord.
The future of...
The Takeda is lost to me.
You must lead them, Yukimura.
Me?!
Farewell, young cub.
[sighs]
[SANADA]
Lordship?
[SANADA gasps]
[SANADA]
No! This can't be happening!
How can you be dead?!
[SARUTOBI] What on earth are
you still doing back here?
[gasps]
Our spearmen are
in total disarray!
--If we don't rally soon--!
--[SANADA] Lord Takeda, he...
[gasps]
We've lost more than a fight.
[SANADA]
Don't leave us!
The Takeda need you!
And so do I!
Men of Takeda! Full retreat!
[SHIMAZU]
Have at ya!
Ya got some stones!
Huh? Turnin' tail?
Hey!
Get'cher ass
back here, Tadakatsu!
[TAKEDA SOLDIERS gasp]
Tell me. Why have
they given up so easily?
Not sure.
[TOKUGAWA]
Takeda's far stronger than this.
There's an ill breeze
comin' in windward.
[gasps]
[CHOSOKABE]
Saints preserve us!
Shige! Bekunosuke!
[growls]
My sons o' bitches!
[YASUBEI]
Captain.
[CHOSOKABE]
Yasubei!
Who's the fiend what did this?
The Tokugawa.
Are you sure of it?
Forgive us.
We should've fought
harder for ya.
Hey! Don't you spout
that bilge-water!
Damn it! Yasubei!
[grunting]
[CHOSOKABE]
Ieyasu's colors.
[TOKUGAWA pants]
[CHOSOKABE]
Heh. Not your first dust-up.
[TOKUGAWA]
Yours neither.
[huffs] Hey. Whaddya say
we make like allies?
I reckon we're just
wastin' powder by now.
All right! From now on,
we fight as one!
[gasps] Just like that,
we're bunkmates?
[TOKUGAWA]
What's the matter?
This was your idea.
It was. I know.
But this is our first
time tradin' broadsides.
Who's to say my
offer is seaworthy?
All I need do to gauge
your trustworthiness
is look to your men.
Once you've given
your word, it's ironclad.
Aye!
[chuckling]
[CHOSOKABE]
Damn yer eyes, Ieyasu!
You back-stabbing cur!
[grunts]
Why'd you do it?
Why?!
[MORI]
It's about time.
[OTANI]
Forgive me.
There is much that keeps
me busy, both near and far.
[MORI] You've consolidated
your power during the chaos.
Well played.
[OTANI]
I'm afraid, my dear comrade,
I don't understand.
With the demise of
Toyotomi and Takenaka,
their influence falls to you.
[MORI scoffs]
Very well.
All that matters
now is what we can do
in the momentous days ahead.
[OTANI giggles] Spread word
of Tokugawa's villainies.
And let it be known
that we have assumed
the mantle of righteousness.
The others will
flock to our side.
[MORI] You are a fine one
to speak of villainy, Otani.
[OTANI]
Chosokabe would have rallied to
Tokugawa's banner,
had we not acted.
The truth of it should
be plain as day to him.
Instead, he puts stock in what
he sees, no matter how contrary.
[giggles]
[MORI] Otani, Chosokabe,
Ishida, Tokugawa.
Your petty machination
bore me to tears.
This country can go
hang for all I care.
I have but a single
concern in this.
The House of Mori.
I will secure my
corner of the board.
Lord Shingen's men scattered.
I wonder why.
Ieyasu.
[TOKUGAWA]
Hm?
Our advance scouts we sent ahead
are reporting no signs
of traps or ambushes.
We should pursue them now!
While they're weak!
[TOKUGAWA gasps]
Wait.
Is that?
That shadow.
--[TOKUGAWA SOLDIERS gasp]
--[TOKUGAWA] Fall back!
Get away from that maelstrom!
[TENKAI giggles]
Why, Lady O-Ichi, there you are.
[KOBAYAKAWA]
Heya, Tenkai!
Let's do a mushroom
hot pot tonight, yeah?
[ICHI]
♪Searching, ever searching♪
[gasps]
It can't be!
[ICHI]
♪many thousand leagues.♪
[ICHI sighs]
Life and death.
There's nary a difference.
Lady O-Ichi.
Could it really be her?
Lord Nobunaga's younger sister.
She survived the carnage.
Who are you? Tell me.
[ICHI]
You are radiant.
Blindingly bright.
[ICHI sighs]
What the?
Ieyasu!
[ICHI sighs]
Look at that darkness.
It's beautiful.
[ICHI] Light and dark shall
clash and melt together,
and oblivion shall issue forth.
My Lord Kenshin.
Takeda Shingen.
[UESUGI grunts]
[KASUGA] He succumbed to
illness in the midst of battle.
[UESUGI] Our shared fate
has been ripped asunder,
it would seem.
The heavens have made
their wishes known,
that men such as us are not
needed in the coming carnage.
[SANADA sobs]
I can see it, guys!
Big Boss's castle!
Thank Buddha!
--[DATE SOLDIERS cheer]
--[KATAKURA gasps]
[cheering continues]
Ishida. Mitsunari.
[NARRATOR]
Next time, "Alliances."