Mitsunari.
[ISHIDA growls]
Ieyasu.
[TOKUGAWA]
Mitsunari.
I do not blame you
for despising me.
What I have done to you is
certainly worthy of your ire.
[ISHIDA]
Shut up!
Somehow,
Lord Hideyoshi found
you to be worthy.
As did Lord Hanbei.
And you betrayed them!
For that crime, you deserve
a thousand deaths!
I will not apologize.
My answer
will be in the future
that I build!
[ISHIDA]
You are a bastard, Ieyasu.
How much more will you mock
me before you are satisfied?
Come at me then!
Prepare to meet your death!
[ISHIDA]
Ieyasu!
[TOKUGAWA]
Mitsunari!
[SOLDIERS murmuring]
[KATAKURA]
Lord Masamune.
It has begun.
[DATE]
Yeah, this thing right here.
It ain't gonna end till
one of 'em's dead.
[TOKUGAWA grunts]
[TOKUGAWA yells]
[ISHIDA yells]
Lord Tokugawa.
Master Ishida.
[TOKUGAWA, ISHIDA grunting]
[ISHIDA]
Bow before my Lord!
Crave his forgiveness!
Beg for it!
And then prepare
to lose your head!
I shall do no such thing!
[TOKUGAWA, ISHIDA grunt]
[ISHIDA]
Damn it.
This is the kind of man
you have always been.
[TOKUGAWA]
Good work on the patrols.
The protection you provide him
allows Lord Hideyoshi to
rest with his mind at ease.
Ah.
We're depending on you men.
[TOYOTOMI SOLDIER A gasps]
Yessir!
Tell me, Ieyasu.
How can you say such
insincere things?
You wound me to call
them insincere.
Then you are a liar.
[TOKUGAWA]
Mitsunari, don't be like this.
Why not offer words of
appreciation once in a while?
Even if my words are insincere?
[ISHIDA] I do not find pleasure
in such false platitudes.
[TOKUGAWA]
You are incredible.
You always look truth
straight in the face.
[ISHIDA]
What are you saying?
Mitsunari, I respect
that look in your eyes.
Thanks to your straight-ahead
gaze, you will keep me honest.
Ever under your watch.
[TOKUGAWA gasps]
[ISHIDA] No matter how
strong an army you raise.
No matter what pretty
excuses you spout.
What these eyes have seen
are your crimes, Ieyasu!
Mitsunari.
[ISHIDA grunts]
Now, Ieyasu!
Answer me!
Why did you betray our Lord?!
Why did you take
Lord Hideyoshi's life?!
[TOKUGAWA]
Mitsunari.
You must have known it, too.
That had we continued,
the fighting would have never
stopped, not for all eternity.
No more.
We cannot climb these stairs
of conflict any longer!
[ISHIDA]
Enough!
This is your delusion.
All you desired
was this country.
For your own greed!
And you simply usurped the
country from Lord Hideyoshi!
You are a filthy thief!
You dressed up your own
ambition, called it a "dream,"
and desecrated Lord
Hideyoshi's rule!
If you say that that is
my crime, I accept it.
However,
what this country needs
is not strength,
but the bonds we share!
More lies!
The only thing you realized
was you desired the country
purely through ugly,
self-righteous ambition!
[ISHIDA gasping]
[ISHIDA] That is why you
have gone on and on!
"The bonds we share"
is a lie to cover up
that greed in your heart!
Admit it!
There is no truth to
the bonds you speak of!
I will not.
Because I know
you've felt it, too.
That one true bond
you and I share.
Stop it!
Bonds this. Bonds that.
Always bonds!
Common bonds, bonds
we share, true bonds.
I'm sick of it all!
Bonds, bonds, bonds, bonds!
Bonds...
[ISHIDA]
I do not accept this.
I will by no means permit it!
I will be damned if I allow
such lies to stand!
Mitsunari.
[ISHIDA] I imagine you
feel satisfied with that.
[ISHIDA]
But as for me,
you already stole the one
bond I cherished most.
How am I supposed to live?!
What should I have done?!
[TOKUGAWA]
Was there no path
where you could have
moved forward with me?
Do not...
Do not say it!
Do not spew any more words!
Enough!
With one hand, you
offer a common bond,
but with the other, you destroy
my bond with Lord Hideyoshi!
What am I to make of it?
This arrogant heart of
yours so full of deceit?!
[Answer me, Ieyasu!
Where does this paradox lead?
No matter what anyone says, I
will never abandon my bonds!
Just watch me go!
I will build this
country's peace!
[ISHIDA]
I will not yield.
Not to you.
To the very moment of my death,
I will not forgive you!
[TOKUGAWA] Then, it seems
I cannot make you understand.
Lay his bonds bare.
Wings the color of death!
I forge the river of
time to our future.
My fists are the bridge!
[KATAKURA]
Lord Masamune.
This next blow will likely be--
Yeah, the final one.
But I sure as hell never
wanted an ending like this.
There is no honor here.
There is only sadness.
[ISHIDA yells]
[TOKUGAWA yells]
Vanish forever into the ether!
Tokugawa Ieyasu!
This is our last goodbye!
Ishida Mitsunari!
[TOKUGAWA yells]
Retreat everyone! Retreat!
Fall back, men!
[NARRATOR] Having embroiled the
entire land of the rising sun,
this battle at Sekigahara, which
divided the country in two,
quietly drew to a close.
[NARRATOR] However, there
was no victor to be found.
[SAIKA] Maeda, do you not need
to return to your own land?
I'm the clan's vagabond
black sheep, remember?
I go where the wind blows.
Leaf on the wind.
I see.
Magoichi, you guys helped
me more than you can know.
My thanks.
[SAIKA laughs]
There's no need for thanks.
Only the payment,
as per our contract.
I dunno what you're...
Oh! Right!
I vaguely recall
somethin' like that.
See, I totally thought, uh...
--[KEIJI chuckles]
--Laughing won't save you.
[BOTH gasp]
[SAIKA]
I should've known.
Are you telling me
you cannot pay?
[KEIJI]
No!
No, no, no, no, no!
I so can't...
[SAIKA]
If that is the case,
you will pay with your body.
Wha...?
[SAIKA] You will work
for the rest of your life
as a member of the Saika Folk.
Repair work, laundry,
housework, cleaning.
Sweeping the yard--
[KEIJI]
Anything but that!
Oh!
Look, a new wind!
It's blowing me in the
direction of a new romance!
So long, Magoichi!
Yumekichi?
[YUMEKICHI chirps]
[SAIKA]
Hmph.
[OTANI]
I...
I am alive?
[OTANI]
Mitsunari.
[NARRATOR] In this fleeting
moment of peace,
those who fought at and
survived Sekigahara
had once again begun
to live their lives.
[OTOMO]
Hooray, Muneshige!
Xavi Land is finally
ready to open!
What is all this?
And behold!
Revolution is the dancer!
[TACHIBANA]
It's all so garish.
Won't be spending
much time here.
[OTOMO]
Muneshige.
Starting today,
you are Jumbo Xavi!
[yelps]
[KURODA]
So fellas!
It's come to my attention
that you didn't have the key!
I've made a humble mistake!
So please?
Let me down!
Why does this always
happen to me?!
[HOJO]
Well, well!
The illustrious Hojo family
will be restored to glory!
I've finally caught up with you!
[gasps]
Ah!
--[TSURUHIME screams]
--[HOJO gasping]
[UESUGI] You will deliver
this letter for me?
[KASUGA]
Yessir.
My Most Beautiful Blade.
Lord Kenshin, my love.
[moans] Lord Kenshin, my love!
Heave-ho, you sons-o'-bitches!
[CHOSOKABE SOLDIERS]
Aye-aye, Captain!
I'm sorry, Your Lordship.
But I must ask to borrow
your troops once more.
Well, Commander,
we're all set to go
to war when you are.
Then let us be off then.
All right, Kojuro.
I'm not turnin' to look
behind me ever again.
I'm countin' on you
to have my back.
Yes, Sir!
You just keep moving
forward with your gaze
fixed firmly upon the heavens!
Here we go!
The party over this
country's back on!
[SANADA yells]
[DATE yells]
[BOTH grunting]
Tell me, Sanada Yukimura.
How ya like my lineup?
My allies has come no
less well-prepared!
[SANADA] As this great
battle draws upon us,
we have all been enveloped
in the greatest
sense of exaltation!
[DATE]
Hell, yeah!
Looks like the second stage
is gonna be a lotta fun!
Heh. Here I come, Sanada!
Masamune!
[DATE grunts]
Sanada, you have given the
signal for the start of war.
I will proudly lead
the vanguard!
[OTANI laughs] Then I will serve
as the battlefield tactician.
Make sure you find a good
spot for me out there, yeah?
Destruction's up my alley!
[ISHIDA grunts]
[laughs]
[SARUTOBI]
Well, we've thrown in
with quite the
idiosyncratic bunch.
Yes.
We are very much a wild
and eccentric lot.
Yet all have come together
for this battle.
To face what is in their hearts.
To look straight
on to our future!
That is the spirit that our
Western Forces rally under!
[SOLDIERS cheer]
[laughs] Aw, the little
cub's all grown up!
[TOKUGAWA] You're the same
as ever, One-Eyed Dragon.
You're truly an
interesting man.
When it comes to parties,
I say the more
interesting, the better.
[KATAKURA]
It's true.
With Sanada and Ishida
and even Chosokabe,
we can have no complaints
regarding to our opponents.
[DATE]
Yeah.
[DATE] Whenever I feel lost,
I just come here.
I look to that tree as a guide
and plant my feet on the ground.
Then I look for the path that
makes some kinda sense to me.
[DATE]
Huh?
One-Eyed Dragon, look!
Your Lordship!
Salutations!
Tiger of the West!
Sanada Yukimura!
And Dragon of the East.
Date Masamune!
[TAKEDA] Upon hearing
the victor of this battle
will rule the land
of the rising sun,
we could no longer remain
silent on the matter.
[UESUGI]
Both the Tiger of Kai and I
intend to prevail
in this battle.
We have formed an alliance
and will challenge the victor
to meet at Kawanakajima, and
do battle to rule this land.
[laughs]
Time to run riot, War God!
At last.
Lord Kenshin, my love.
[TAKEDA]
On me!
All units, advance!
[UESUGI SOLDIERS yell]
[SARUTOBI] I swear, does
he know brash or what?
So what now, Commander?
[SANADA]
You buffoon!
[SARUTOBI groaning]
[SANADA]
Though it be from His Lordship,
as the commander,
my only response to such an
earnest challenge is to accept!
Ow!
Right, Sanada.
On this field, you're
the Supreme Commander
of the Western Forces.
Now is the time to fulfill your
promise to set my spirit ablaze!
It will be my honor!
I am Sanada Yukimura, Western
Forces Supreme Commander.
Join me.
And set alight the
fires within you all!
[SOLDIERS cheer]
Sanada leading the
Western Forces.
Lord Shingen and the War God.
Formidable opponents,
are they not?
Indeed.
But 'the crazier the
better' is the Date way.
[DATE chuckles]
[ALL yelling]
Ieyasu, Kojuro,
have fun out there.
Date Masamune, Big
Boss o' the East!
Full speed ahead!
[SOLDIERS cheer]
It's an endless party!
[DATE yells]