[NARRATOR]
The Sengoku Period,
a time of chaos and bloodshed.
In this period
of warring states,
dozens of feudal lords
vied for supremacy,
hoping to unite this
land of the rising sun.
Fate, once set in motion.
can be stopped by no one.
Our current course will
take us straight into lands
under Sanada's protection, sire!
[scoffs]
[DATE] I'll knock him
on his ass if I have to!
[SARUTOBI] As we
were telling Otani,
the Takeda want to
partner up with you.
[NARRATOR]
Fate, set in motion.
[DATE]
Ishida.
[DATE] Fill your hands,
you son of a bitch!
[NARRATOR] With all
roads, leading to Sekigahara.
And you are, who again?
[gasps]
[DATE]
Bastard!
Think back to Odawara.
Odawara?
[DATE]
That's right!
We fought a duel that day!
It was epic, dammit!
[ISHIDA]
That day...
You bore me. Begone, fool.
[grunts]
[gasps]
[DATE]
Ishida!
[DATE yells]
[grunts]
Sanada! Get outta my way!
Never!
Master Ishida is a guest
here under my protection!
I would die before I
let harm befall him!
[DATE]
Is that so?
All right.
I'll start this party off
by killing you first!
[BOTH grunting]
[yells]
[DATE, SANADA grunting]
[SANADA] This cold,
hollow style of fighting.
It is not like you!
[yells]
[DATE]
When it's kill or be killed,
I'm "like" whatever
I need to be!
[yells]
[grunting]
"Kill or be".
Dammit, Lord Dat--
No, don't.
This is a fight
these two generals
have chosen for themselves.
You're the Dragon's
Right Eye.
Did Odawara... cloud your
vision just like his?
[gasps]
You're worthless!
You don't really think
you can stop me?!
[SANADA, DATE grunting]
Childish.
[DATE growls]
Ishida!
[SANADA] I am the opponent
you face at this time!
Wait! We haven't even talked
about our alliance yet!
Per Gyobu counsel,
I have met with the
commander of the Takeda
and proposed an alliance.
He may reply at
Lord Hideyoshi's castle.
[DATE]
Ishida, wait! Ishida!
Move it, Sanada!
No, my rival.
Though it may cost me
my life, I will not yield!
[DATE] You wanna
pay with your life,
I'm happy to collect!
[SANADA grunts]
[DATE yells]
Lord Masamune.
[SANADA yells]
Raging Flames!
[DATE grunts]
Damn it! His wounds
have reopened!
[SANADA, DATE grunting]
Ishida!
[grunting]
Lord Masamune!
[SARUTOBI grunts]
[DATE]
Magnum Strike!
[SANADA, DATE grunting]
[SARUTOBI]
Commander!
[SANADA, SARUTOBI grunt]
Now die.
I won't let you do this!
[yells]
[DATE gasps]
Lord Masamune,
that is far enough!
Let me go, Kojuro!
My blades haven't reached
Ishida's throat!
[KATAKURA]
Nor will they!
Take a good look.
[gasps]
[DATE gasps]
I'm done with you, Sanada.
[KATAKURA grunts]
Lord Masamune.
[groans]
[KATAKURA]
Lord Masamune.
Let us return to Oshu for a
time and rethink our strategy.
No, Kojuro.
The answer is "no," all right?
[grunts]
[KATAKURA]
Lord Masamune,
with all that weighs upon you,
how does this world appear
through your eyes?
[NARRATOR] Around the same
time at Osaka Castle,
Otani Yoshitsugu was
charging Chosokabe Motochika
with a mission.
[OTANI]
As you well know,
we have come together to
stop Tokugawa's brutality,
as he plots to usurp this
country from all of us.
But by heavens' mercy,
he is moving quickly.
Enough with the
flowery speeches, Gyobu.
What do we need to do?
[OTANI] Actually, I hope
you might do me a favor.
It will require travel to
Kyushu in the far south.
Kyushu?
[OTANI]
We need pieces on the board.
Shimazu and Kuroda.
Otomo is another story,
but his retainer, Tachibana,
should prove useful.
Should Tokugawa ever
succeed in taking Kyushu,
it would keep us hopelessly
pinned down in Osaka.
In other words,
go an' recruit everyone in
the west over to our side.
Leave it to me.
[OTANI]
That said,
visiting them all yourself
would be quite arduous.
Hence the favor.
Work with Mori to see
that it gets done.
[CHOSOKABE]
Mori?
I've gone at it with him
more times'n I can count!
He ain't the kind
of son-of-a-bitch
you can play nice with!
Sorry pal, that's a
deal breaker!
[OTANI]
Time is not a luxury we have.
This, too, is for the sake
of bringing down Tokugawa.
[CHOSOKABE growls]
[NARRATOR]
Aki.
The largest harbor facing
the Inland Sea of Seto.
And the stronghold
of Mori Motonari,
who rules the western
end of Honshu.
[hammering]
[footsteps]
[MORI]
Well, Chosokabe.
Yeah I know.
I'm ain't thrilled to see
your ugly mug either.
But this poor harbor's uglier.
The hell happened here?
Much like the grief which
recently befell Shikoku,
we suffered a sneak attack
by one who schemes
to seize the country.
The architect of our
woe is Tokugawa Ieyasu.
Ieyasu was here, too?
[MORI]
So what brings you here?
Come to take Aki
while we are down?
Nah.
I'll come back n' settle things
with you after I crush Ieyasu!
Actually, Otani sent
me out here.
So, you have joined forces
with Ishida as well.
What errand did Otani give you?
[CHOSOKABE]
He said to work with you
to get all the folks in
Kyushu on board with us.
I assume he refers to Kuroda,
Shimazu, and Otomo.
You deal with the Otomo brat.
I'll go take care of
Kuroda and Shimazu.
Otomo... Lovely.
Oh, since we're allies,
I'm borrowin' one o' your ships.
Might have ta spruce her up
a bit pirate-style, though.
[MORI chuckles]
People sure change,
don't they, Ieyasu?
[NARRATOR]
The land of Owari.
Once a gleaming
paragon of prosperity,
it fell to ruin with the
decline of the house of Oda.
Now, all that remained was
Owari Castle's burnt husk.
Which sheltered the tattered
remnants of the Oda Clan.
Visiting them,
was Tokugawa Ieyasu.
You hold Lady O-Ichi hostage
and dare threaten us further?
Lady O-Ichi is safe
at Sunpu Castle.
And I would never
threaten you valiant men.
In fact, I wish for you to
join us in moving forward!
First, you betrayed the Oda
for the Toyotomi and now,
you hope to rule the
country yourself?
Return Lady O-Ichi to us!
Offer up the country to the Oda!
That is how you can
"move forward!"
Now, listen.
[ODA REMNANT 5A]
You traitor!
[ODA REMNANT 5B]
Give Lady O-Ichi back!
[ODA REMNANTS shouting]
[NARRATOR]
Meanwhile,
working in the service
of Saika Magoichi.
Tsuruhime was
searching for Ieyasu
and had entered the
land of Odawara.
Aw! I'm s'posed to
have a fateful encounter
in the deep dark woods.
My divinations told me so.
Yeah, well it seems
like fate to me!
--[OUTLAWS laugh]
--[HOJO] Toriya!
Ieyasu?
[HOJO yells]
[OUTLAWS gasp]
[HOJO] How dare you waylay
a helpless young maiden?
And you once called
yourselves warriors?
[OUTLAW 5A]
Who the hell's this old geezer?
Elderly Sir,
are you the one I'm?
Fear not, miss. You just
leave these thugs to me.
With this, my family heirloom,
the Hojo Spear of--
--aargh!
--[cracking]
--[TSURUHIME shouts]
--[HOJO groans]
Elderly Sir!
I am so sorry,
young lady.
Just get off!
[OUTLAW 5A] He made
things easier for us!
[OUTLAWS laugh]
What do I do?
[gasps]
Hold on, that's.
[OUTLAWS gasp]
Goodness, you're just...
You're dead meat!
[yells]
[OUTLAWS grunting]
[grunts, groans]
Dang it all.
[gasps]
[TSURUHIME] From the gloaming,
he gallantly appears!
Like a dancing feather,
he saves me!
Truly! You are the one I was
destined to meet this day!
[giggles]
Waitaminnit.
Where in the world, did he go?
[TOKUGAWA]
So many derelict villages.
So many men, with no
place to call home.
It is clear we've not
a moment to lose
in ending this time of war.
Oh! Good. Ieyasu!
[TOKUGAWA] Wait, you're the
Cloaked Shrine Maiden
of the Kouno of Iyo!
What are you doing here?
I was out looking for you
because I have some questions.
You may ask whatever
you'd like.
Oh, good. Then I
won't hold back.
What was your intention
in trying to recruit
my dear lady Magoichi?
Do you mean to make
her fight on the frontlines,
as might be expected?
Are you certain you
haven't kidnapped anyone?
And really. Are you a
good person or a bad one?
Where is this all going?
Would you mind asking those
questions one at a time?
[grunts]
This is too much trouble!
I'll put the questions
to your future!
Prithee, heed me!
Take that!
[gasps]
That should be answer enough.
Ieyasu. I don't get it.
What are you trying to do?
[SANADA grunting]
[gasps]
[SARUTOBI]
Ah, Commander, excellent,
it's good you're finally awake.
[SANADA]
W-What of Lord Masamune?
[SARUTOBI]
Dunno.
To think Master Katakura
stepped in and saved my life.
It seems like they've got
plenty problems of their own
to sort out.
And what of Lord Ishida?
He returned to Osaka.
I see. I was certainly
quite the disgraceful sight.
However. That was not the
Lord Masamune I know.
Our past battles sparked
such fire in my heart.
But not this time.
Things've changed between you.
Before, you two
were simply warriors
who shared a mutual
respect for one another.
But Lord Date,
was just a man out
for revenge this time.
You can't fill your own shoes
as commander of this army.
A man only half-fledged.
And a man only half-fledged,
can never command.
It is true.
[NARRATOR] It was assumed
that Date Masamune
was headed for Osaka Castle,
in pursuit of Ishida Mitsunari.
However...
Lord Masamune,
it is reckless to continue on
to Osaka Castle from here.
I urge you to reconsider.
Who said we were
going after Ishida?
Next stop, is Sunpu!
[gasps]
[DATE]
All these whiny bastards,
with their "Ieyasu this"
and "Ieyasu that".
Hell, I'll just go
crush him myself!
See how they like that!
You seriously intend
to fight with Tokugawa?
[DATE]
Damn straight!
And you keep your
nose out of it.
As my injured Right Eye,
just shut up and watch.
[NARRATOR] Chosokabe had
been tasked with recruiting
the Kyushu clans and so
found himself paying a visit
to Shimazu Yoshihiro,
ruler of Satsuma.
I reckoned someone'd be comin'
to see me before too long.
But I'm surprised it's the
Ogre 'o the Western Sea.
Well, I know they call
you an ogre too, Shimazu.
Thought we could find out
who's worthy of the name!
You started hackin' away
'fore y'even asked me
whatcha came to ask!
[laughs]
Best way to get through that
thick skull o' yours, I figure?
So yeah. Wanna join up
with the Western Forces?
Yer a right interestin' man,
Ogre o' the Western Sea.
[BOTH grunting]
What sorta man's Ishida
that someone like
you'd follow 'is lead?
Mopey son-of-a-bitch
is honest to a fault!
He wants to beat that
Ieyasu bastard to a pulp!
Just like I do!
[SHIMAZU]
Oh yeah?
[CHOSOKABE] All us
sons-of-bitches with Ishida
got the same goal!
I hear even Sanada Yukimura of
the Takeda wants Ieyasu's head!
Really? The Tiger's
young cub, too?
Hold up. You tellin'
me you know Sanada?
Sounds like things're shapin' up
to get real hairy in the middle.
Awright! I believe
I will take yer side!
Whuh?
I smell a big ol' war a-brewin'.
This oughtta be my
chance to settle things
with the greatest damn
warrior from out west.
We'll fight fer who gets
to be "Ogre" after the war!
[laughs]
Gotta say. You're awful
spry for a guy your age.
[NARRATOR]
Around that time.
Otomo Sorin, who boasts
great power in Kyushu,
saw flocking to him
many believers of Xavism,
a mysterious religion that
had swept across the land.
[TACHIBANA]
Lord Mori.
We appreciate you taking the
trouble to come all this--
Ah, wonderful!
I have longed to
meet you, Tactician!
No, wait. Sunday!
I... "Sunday?" "Tactician?"
It can't be.
You're suffering amnesia!
[gasps] What a dramatic and
unfortunate turn of events!
Of what do you speak, young sir?
Yes, of course, this is simply
Lord Xavi's way of testing me.
I see, Lord.
You're telling me this time,
I must bring Sunday
into the fold myself!
Oh! We'll have Lord
Xavi in the center.
Sunday!
Chesty!
Joshy!
And, of course.
There's me!
[chuckles]
Oh, how dreamy this'll be!
[OTOMO]
Oh! Lord Xavi!
[TACHIBANA] Great. Now this
guy is looking at us
like we're totally crazy
town banana pants.
[MORI]
We are done talking.
My heart is
passionately urging me
not to stay a single
moment longer.
Farewell.
[OTOMO]
Just watch, Lord Xavi.
I shall overcome this test!
[NARRATOR]
Having left Satsuma,
Chosokabe Motochika moved on.
Next on his list
was Kuroda Kanbei.
Awright, I'll just
get to the point.
Kuroda Kanbei, will you join
sides with Ishida Mitsunari?
[KURODA]
Ishida, you say?
[CHOSOKABE]
Yeah, And Otani, too.
Mitsunari? And Gyobu?
Hell no!
A request coming
from the bastards
who stuffed my humble
self in to this hole?
I'll never do it!
Well now. No one saw fit
to mention this to me.
Bastards sent me full sail into
a hell of a mess on this voyage.
Take a look at
this damn thing!
Ever since this got put on,
my humble self's luck has
gotten worse and worse!
I may not look it,
but back in the day,
I was hailed as the clever one
of Toyotomi's two strategists!
But that Gyobu bastard
got jealous and...
Anyway, I refuse to
do anything they want!
If you want to ask my
humble self for something,
bring me the damn key
to these damn shackles!
The key? Does Otani
have it or what?
Gyobu told me that he
dropped it during battle!
What the hell?
Can't you be more
responsible keeping track
of things like this?
Sounds like you've
been through a lot, too.
You really understand?
You seem like a stand up guy!
I have an idea!
I know someone who might help
us find where the key is.
You do? Who's that?
Leggy lil' lass who's
good at divinations.
Hang with me, and I bet
she'll be the one to find us.
So, yeah?
You wanna join forces
with me and find a clue?
[growls] Those bastards
really tick me off, but,
This'll be for the key to
these shackles! All right!
I'll join you!
[TOKUGAWA] I take it that
your coming here means
that you have decided to
become allies with me,
One-Eyed Dragon.
Ha. Sorry, that's not the plan.
I'm just here to crush you.
So there's no one else
between me and Ishida
[grunts]
I won't let anyone
else interfere!
What say we go at it one-on-one!
Very well then.
You stay put, too, Tadakatsu.
[grunts]
[yells]
Your sword!
I have no need of swords!
With these fists, I will
forge a bond with you!
Ha! You don't wanna
mess with me!
One-Eyed Dragon.
I wish I had known you before as
the straight as an arrow cynic
with his eyes on the prize.
That Dragon fell to earth!
And a dragon ain't much good
crawling on the ground.
I've changed, Ieyasu.
The guy you want doesn't exist!
In that case, why don't you make
a wager with me on this fight.
[DATE]
Wager?
The terms are, if I win,
you change once more!
[gasps]
Makes no difference.
I'm not gonna lose ever again!
[DATE yelling]
Where is your fire,
One-Eyed Dragon?
Your attacks have no bite!
[KATAKURA grunts]
[DATE grunts]
Shut up!
[yells]
[DATE grunts]
[grunts]
[KATAKURA gasps]
I win, Dragon.
[grunts]
Not yet!
[grunting]
[gasps]
Do you yield now?
[grunts]
Masamune.
[NARRATOR]
Next time. "Declarations."