[NARRATOR]
The Sengoku Period,
a time of chaos and bloodshed.
In this period
of warring states,
dozens of feudal lords
vied for supremacy,
hoping to unite this
land of the rising sun.
Some fought as though blind,
having lost sight of
their righteous cause.
[NARRATOR] But those
battles would only serve
to push away their
friends and comrades.
Masamune.
[NARRATOR]
High and low, strife abounded.
With all roads,
leading to Sekigahara.
[TOKUGAWA] Time will cure
whatever ails him.
[KATAKURA]
No.
But this will.
Up, Masamune!
[gasps]
[KATAKURA grunts]
[grunts]
You can lie down when
you're dead, One-Eyed Dragon!
Their friendship
is a unique one.
[DATE]
What the hell, Kojuro?
Shut up!
[grunts]
Did you forget what you
learned that fateful day?
That lesson, bought with blood?
What day?
[KATAKURA]
Your first battle.
[SOLDIERS yelling]
[DATE SOLDIER 6A]
Big Boss!
Our allies have all fled!
This position will be
overrun any minute now!
[DATE]
Bastards! Hold your ground!
Lord Masamune,
it's time to go.
[DATE]
I'm staying right here!
This is Oshu's first big party
with the One-Eyed Dragon!
I ain't runnin'!
[KATAKURA] What does it
prove if your first battle
is also your last, my lord?
[DATE chuckles]
Proves I got a pair!
So what if I die?
Beats the hell outta
turning tail, don't it?
Our losses mean nothing
if you perish here!
If I run now, they're gonna
think I'm nothing but hot air!
Yes, and it pains me.
[DATE SOLDIER 6A] Please,
Big Boss, sound the retreat!
We are not leaving here!
[gasps]
[yelling]
[DATE SOLDIER 6B]
Defend the Big Boss!
[DATE SOLDIER 6C]
Yeah!
[DATE SOLDIER 6D]
Please, my lord!
No retreat!
[SOLDIERS grunting]
Masamune!
[DATE]
Huh?!
[thudding]
[DATE grunting]
[sobs]
[KATAKURA]
Listen well, Masamune.
I do not fear meeting my end.
But never in the heat of
battle have I wanted to die!
[gasps]
Lord Masamune.
Oshu's hopes all rest upon you.
But we reap what you sow.
Look upon what you have wrought.
[gasps]
[DATE] You said. "I do
not fear meeting my end.
But never in the heat of
battle have I wanted to die."
Bontenmaru needed
to hear that.
So did the One-Eyed Dragon.
Your lordship.
I shall depart for Osaka Castle.
I am only half a leader.
My faults run as deep
as ever they did.
[SANADA shouts]
[shouts continue]
[SANADA gasps]
That was far too close!
You know, most people
practice during the day.
Sasuke.
You've seen our lord's
mission through to the end?
That's right. Doing it
quickly and correctly
is sort of the Sarutobi
Sasuke calling card.
Incidentally, that was the
last mission on your plate.
Since you're in charge,
Master Sanada,
I guess you've inherited us.
Whatever you may need us
to do, just say the word.
You answer to me?
[SARUTOBI]
I do.
But whoever calls the shots
must prove himself worthy.
Let's see what you can do!
Wait! I wasn't ready yet!
Of course not.
I want to see what you can
do at the drop of a hat.
Not when you're expecting it!
If that's what you came
here for, very well!
[SARUTOBI]
Yeah! That's the spirit!
[yells]
He's using a decoy!
[SARUTOBI]
If that caught you by surprise,
then we can just
call it a night.
[SANADA]
And now illusions?
Go on.
I'll cut through all of them!
[SANADA gasps]
For the record,
you'd be missing a head
if this were a real fight.
[SANADA grunts]
[SARUTOBI]
This is a problem.
If you can't deliver, my men and
I will end up without a master.
[growls]
I found you, Sasuke!
[SARUTOBI grunts]
Job well done!
[stuttering]
[SANADA]
So? Did I pass your test?
Yeah. You seem
pretty worthy, more or less.
You don't sound very sure.
No one's doubting
you've got guts.
But you're just
way too reckless.
I'm just saying.
[grunts]
I know that, someday,
I will become a leader
that Lord Takeda and you
can be proud of, Sasuke!
Said like a lord of Kai.
As of today...
...we're the Sanada
Ninja Corp, at your service.
[gasps]
[SANADA] I gave him my word and
now I must make good on it!
Master, would you like me to
join you on your trip to Osaka?
[SANADA]
No. It's better if I go alone.
[SARUTOBI]
All right.
I'll keep an eye
on the place for ya.
[SARUTOBI] He's heading off into
the jungle by his lonesome.
Happy hunting, young Tiger.
Earn your stripes.
[TSURUHIME]
Hm?
Huh...
I gotta tell Lady Magoichi.
There's sorrow in Iesasu.
Not to mention that darkness.
[TSURUHIME]
The pirate!
Well-met, missy!
I wondered when the trade
winds might blow you by!
[grunts]
I'm not here to fight,
so leave them arrows be.
Wanted to ask you
for a bit of a favor.
I'm listening.
You're that shrine maiden
who gets glimpses
into the future, right?
I beg of you! Do your
hocus-pocus or whatever
and find the key that'll let
me outta these damn things!
Come on!
[TSURUHIME sighs]
All right, but I am in a hurry.
Once I tell you where
to look, off you go.
Prithee heed me!
[gasps]
Here we go!
Huh?
[TSURUHIME sighs]
That was... amazing!
[CHOSOKABE, KURODA]
Hm?
He appears with the wind,
in a rain of black feathers.
And a stalwart
heart skips a beat!
Come again?
"Rain of feathers?"
What the hell?
[gasps]
Could it be?
Their meeting... is destiny!
Pretty vague, i'nit?
So who's the
meeting with, huh?
--Come on! Hey! Cough it up!
--[TSURUHIME whimpers]
If you're really that
hungry for specifics,
I will give them.
I want to tell the world.
[humming]
[TSURUHIME]
There!
He appears at the
moment of greatest need,
saves the day, and leaves
with nary a word!
Hold on. Isn't that the--?
[KURODA]
Whoa! The legendary ninja!
She does knows which
way the wind's gonna blow
a lot of the time.
Why does Fuma have the key for
my shackles in the first place?
Damn it!
All I wanted were
some easy answers,
but it's never easy, is it!
[gasps] Hojo sided with the
eastern guys, isn't that right?
He did.
[KURODA]
Hell, if that's the case,
I'll use those quick wits
of Gyobu's to get key back!
See ya, Western Ogre!
I'm off to Osaka!
Hey, Kuroda! Hold on!
[KURODA] Look out, key!
I'm coming for ya!
I wonder.
When will I see him again?
Uh, thanks?
[ICHI sighs]
How is Lady O-Ichi faring?
Hard to tell, my lord.
She won't talk to anyone,
and she refuses to eat.
It's like we're holding a ghost.
[sighs]
You there. Who are you?
You're as bright as the sun.
[TOKUGAWA]
Please, Milady, eat your food.
If you perish here.
Then your loyal retainers
have served you in vain.
Curious.
Why are you covered in blood?
That's how my
brother used to look.
[gasps]
[SAKAI]
Watch your tongue!
[ICHI gasps]
[TOKUGAWA]
Leave her be.
[gasps]
[grunts]
Hideyoshi, did you
change who Ieyasu was?
[TSURUHIME growls]
Stop following me already!
[CHOSOKABE]
You're not the boss of me!
I'll walk where I please!
[TSURUHIME]
Shouldn't you be on a boat?
Ahoy, vagabond!
I didn't expect to see you here!
[growls]
Oh! Lady Magoichi!
I had a vision!
Ieyasu is hiding something!
Whatever it is,
it's horrible!
I think.
This is all kind of a hunch.
--I knew it!
--[TSURUHIME gasps]
[TSURUHIME]
What?
Listen, Sayaka.
It'd be good to have you aboard.
Whaddya say?
Y'wanna join the Western
Army for old time's sake?
They'll pay ya handsomely!
Sayaka's not a
name I use anymore.
Tell me.
Why do you side with the West?
You and Toyotomi
were bitter foes.
He was a devil, true enough.
But Ieyasu's worse!
[KEIJI]
What happened?
That villain robbed
me of my treasure.
My men!
[KEIJI]
No way!
He'd never do such a thing!
The souls of my poor
sons-of-bitches!
They're crying out
for vengeance!
And why exactly have you pinned
this crime on Tokugawa?
'Cause of this!
They left me their colors!
The bastards who killed
them left this behind
on a pile of broken corpses!
What more proof
does a captain need?
[SAIKA laughs]
You're a fool, you know that?
[grunts]
For a mercenary,
such banners are a useful tool.
In war, you use
whatever you can.
Like the trappings
of another army.
It's one of the oldest tricks
in the book, Chosokabe!
[grunts] But if he
didn't do it, who did?
[SAIKA]
Maybe you should talk to Ieyasu.
[KEIJI, CHOSOKABE grunt]
That's assuming you're
not too scared to do it.
You have the look of a man
who'd rather cling to a mistake
than find out he's a fool.
[gasps]
Who are you calling a fool?
I'll show you a mistake!
[KEIJI grunts]
[CHOSOKABE grunts]
Magoichi.
You're a straight-shooter
in more ways than one.
Mind if I tag along?
[CHOSOKABE]
Hm?
[KEIJI] Maybe my absence'll
make the heart grow fonder.
[laughs]
All kidding aside, though,
we both need to talk to him.
My lady.
We'll see it through.
[TOKUGAWA] Clouds are
not all that shut out
the light of the sun.
People lock their
hearts in the darkness.
Tadakatsu.
I swear.
I will bring this land together.
Our future is a united one.
He will pay.
[SHIMAZU]
Ah, tiger cub.
Looks like you grew up a
bit since last I seen ya.
Lord Shimazu!
Shingen always used to tell me.
Watching the young'uns
you put stock in grow up?
That's the greatest
joy a man can have.
[laughs]
I never knew him to
say such a thing.
I thank you for letting me know.
[SHIMAZU] Come to see
Master Ishida, huh?
Yes.
Before I can call
Master Ishida my ally,
there's something that
I need to ask him.
One general to another.
[footsteps]
[ISHIDA]
Hm?
Master Ishida.
Answer me this one question.
What are your plans for
this country, after the war?
"After the war," eh?
Honestly, I couldn't care less.
What the--?
But were you not entrusted
with Toyotomi's legacy?
How will you rule
a unified land?
Why would I burden
myself with it?
I value nothing but
Ieyasu's head on a pike.
[ISHIDA]
Oh, Ieyasu.
By the time I am done with you,
death will be a mercy
you'll beg me to dispense!
That's all it is?
Do you think Lord
Hideyoshi would wish for you
to demean yourself
with some petty vendetta!
Take these words to heart.
[gasps]
Do not speak of
my lord's desires!
[yells]
[ISHIDA grunts]
[BOTH grunting]
I already lost to you once.
So whatever happens,
just know this ain't about me
trying to back out
of our alliance.
Then why are we
squaring off again?
You must have some
problem with me, Masamune.
The only problem
I got, is with me!
Check it out.
I'm gonna give you a
real fight this time!
All right!
[grunts]
[Both yell]
Look at you!
How could you ever know my pain?
I know it well!
I too, have lost my master.
And struggled under the weight
of an impossible burden.
You.
You couldn't be more wrong!
[BOTH grunt]
[BOTH yell]
[grunting]
[panting]
[OTANI]
Enough, Ishida.
The Takeda are strong.
As is their general.
[gasps]
[OTANI]
Save your rage for Ieyasu.
[SHIMAZU]
Good fightin'.
[SANADA]
For all of our differences,
Master Ishida and I,
are the same.
[SANADA]
My course is set.
[DATE, TOKUGAWA yelling]
[BOTH grunt]
I'm having a
helluva time, man!
See what I can do when
my head's on straight?
One-Eyed Dragon.
I'm glad you asked
me for a rematch.
[DATE chuckles]
[TOKUGAWA chuckles]
[DATE]
Here we go!
[yells]
[DATE]
Crazy Storm!
[yells, gasps]
[gasps, chuckles]
So, not to be a dick about it,
but I think we're pretty
much on even footing now.
That was all I ever wanted.
[chuckles]
[SANADA]
The Takeda of Kai!
We hereby ally with the West!
[DATE]
Count Oshu in!
My boys love a good party!
We're joining East!
[NARRATOR]
Next time, "Darkness."