[NARRATOR]
The Sengoku Period,
a time of chaos and bloodshed.
In this period of
warring states,
dozens of feudal lords
vied for supremacy,
hoping to unite this
land of the rising sun.
One takes up arms to
regain his wounded pride.
One grapples with the
weight of his lord's mantle.
[NARRATOR] While another's
heart is set ablaze
with loyal vengeance.
And another bloodies his fists
in the name of brotherhood.
One by one,
alliances are forged.
With all roads,
leading to Sekigahara.
[SANADA]
Today, men, we go to war!
[TAKEDA SOLDIERS cheer]
Hold on, master!
What is the meaning of this?
[SANADA] Your timing
couldn't be better, Sasuke.
Come and share in this victory!
What? Who do you mean to fight?
Uesugi Kenshin,
War God of Echigo!
Huh?!
[SANADA] Brave warriors
of Kai, follow me!
[TAKEDA SOLDIERS cheer]
[SARUTOBI]
Hold on a second!
What are you thinking?
[SANADA]
I've come to a realization.
Kai can have no true
ruler but our lord.
But, what's that got
to do with Kenshin?
[SANADA]
Don't you get it?
If our lord is the only
legitimate ruler of Kai,
then I have to adopt the actions
he'd undertake in his stead!
Huh?!
[SANADA] As the vessel
of Takeda's spirit.
I ride to face my rival,
Uesugi Kenshin!
[SANADA]
Onward, men! To glory!
[TAKEDA SOLDIERS cheer]
[SARUTOBI]
Seriously?
[SANADA]
This is Kawanakajima.
My lord and Lord Uesugi have
met here in battle many a time.
Our foe's territory
lies just beyond!
[TAKEDA SOLDIERS cheer]
[gasps]
Why is it snowing?
[SARUTOBI]
Look out!
[grunts]
[TAKEDA SOLDIERS yell]
[SARUTOBI]
So, that happened.
[grunts, gasps]
[TAKEDA SOLDIERS gasp]
I should have guessed.
[UESUGI] I sensed your
approach from miles away.
[SARUTOBI]
Excuse me, War God?
There's something
you should know.
Don't try to explain
my actions away!
[SARUTOBI] Hm? You really mean
to go through with this?
Of course I do. I'm here
on our lord's behalf!
In that case,
do what you're gonna.
Lord Uesugi Kenshin.
I've come to fight you,
man to man!
Here for a duel?
I will oblige you, then.
Let loose the tiger
within your soul.
I, Sanada Genjiro Yukimura,
will defeat you all for
the greater glory of Kai!
[yells]
[UESUGI grunts]
[grunts]
[scoffs]
[SANADA yells] I wield this
axe as my lord's emissary!
You dishonor it with
all this dodging!
[yelling]
[SANADA]
Stand and fight me!
[SANADA grunting]
Turmoil. That is all I
sense as I watch you teeter
under that axe's weight.
[growls]
Are you calling my
resolve into doubt?
[yelling]
[gasps]
[shouts]
[grunts, yells]
[grunts, gasps]
[gasping]
[UESUGI] The Tiger of Kai
is a giant among men.
Why then do you sully his
spirit with this pantomime?
[gasps]
You're right.
My lord would never
be so foolish.
[UESUGI] You were closer
to him than any, and yet.
What can you claim to
know of your master?
Nothing.
[SANADA] All of that
time spent, and I know nothing.
[UESUGI]
What did you learn at his knee?
[SANADA]
Nothing.
His wisdom, was wasted on me.
[grunts]
[UESUGI]
Tell me.
How have you carried yourself?
[grunts]
[SANADA]
All I've done.
Was march along behind him,
and ape his every move.
[gasps]
Forgive me.
[choking]
[gasps]
[pants]
[grunts, coughs]
Feel shame, young tiger.
Shame at your ignorance.
Let it burn until
you are emptied.
And then, when the
flames have subsided...
...take pride in
how you've grown.
Your master was right to entrust
you with the future of Kai.
[SANADA gasps]
What have I done?
The Tiger has not
left this world.
His soul endures in
the heart of the man
with whom he's crossed
blades so many a time.
And in yours, young Yukimura.
[whimpers, sobs]
[SARUTOBI]
That's our guy.
He's nothing if not sincere.
[sobbing continues]
[UESUGI] The Uesugi will
abstain from the current
East-West conflict.
Fight however your
heart leads you,
secure in my guarantee
that we will not attack
the Takeda from behind.
[SARUTOBI]
Hm?
[UESUGI chuckles]
Gotcha.
I'll try to keep him from
going off half-cocked.
[UESUGI]
My most beautiful blade,
lend them the benefit
of your expertise.
Huh?
[UESUGI] Shepherd this
war down its rightful path.
But my lord--
[KASUGA gasps]
No one else can
do this for me.
[gasps]
If it pleases you.
Oh, yes!
Yes, Lord Kenshin!
A thousand times, yes!
What the--?
[TAKEDA SOLDIERS chattering]
[SANADA]
I acted rashly today.
[SARUTOBI]
Hm?
[SANADA] We have
made the right decision.
I, Yukimura, will fight
Lord Tokugawa.
We will regain the pride of
Kai from he who took it.
I am glad to see you've
found your resolve,
Master, but you know...
You needn't say it.
As we stand at present, we have
no chance against Tokugawa.
So our victory depends
on forging an alliance
with another lord.
Master Ishida seems a likely
choice, given their history.
Oh yeah. He hates that guy.
[SANADA] I mean to make for
Osaka Castle straightaway
and present my offer.
Diplomacy's a new tack
for you. That said...
It wouldn't do for you
to appear too eager.
You say here. I'll handle this.
What exactly are
you going to do?
[SARUTOBI]
Don't worry.
I've got it covered.
And, I've got back-up.
[SANADA]
The shinobi ?
[NARRATOR]
Meanwhile,
Tokugawa Ieyasu was
heading for Ujo Castle,
and its master,
Kobayakawa Hideaki.
Aw, how come daikon radish
takes so long to cook
all the way through, huh?
I'm hungry right now!
--[TOKUGAWA clears throat]
--[KOBAYAKAWA] Hm?
[gasps]
[KOBAYAKAWA] Ieyasu!
You're not supposed to be here!
Just go away!
You can't control
who might show up.
No one will blame you.
[KOBAYAKAWA] But if Lord Mori or
Mitsunari were to find you here,
they'd serve you up a
whole banquet of pain!
I know the risk I'm taking.
I came, to ally myself with you.
Let us shake hands
on it, like men.
Nobody ever treats
me like a man!
[MORI] Know your place,
you simpering glutton.
[ISHIDA] Irritate me
and I'll run you through.
[KOBAYAKAWA] But, w-who knows
what they'll do to me
if I betray them!
[KOBAYAKAWA whimpers]
You'll make the choice
that's right for you.
Until then.
What am I gonna do?
Now I'm hungry and confused
and scared, all at once!
[TENKAI]
You're going to be just fine.
Simply... do whatever
you think is right.
Mister Tenkai!
[NARRATOR] News of
Tokugawa Ieyasu's trip
to Ujo Castle reached
Osaka in the blink of an eye.
He what?!
With every breath, he vexes me!
[OTANI] Tokugawa has been ahead
of you at every turn thus far.
[ISHIDA]
Damn your eyes, Ieyasu!
[OTANI] Now it is my
turn to make a move.
[NARRATOR] Having entered
into a spur-of-the-moment
contract with the Saika Faction,
Maeda Keiji remained
in their compound, sifting
through their dispatches
for word of his abducted
sister-in-law, Matsu.
Wet out there.
Tsuruhime still
hasn't returned yet?
[SAIKA] It was her choice to
run off and see Tokugawa.
Yeah. Tell me something.
What do you do with
all these dispatches?
[SAIKA] Battles are won before
armies take to the field.
Thanks to this, we can make
every bullet count.
[KEIJI] That makes sense.
Heard any word from your
informants on Matsu's
whereabouts yet?
Not that I've seen so far.
Sorry.
[SAIKA gasps]
Bad news or what?
[SAIKA] Something's off about
Kobayakawa's troop movement.
He has soldiers?
[whimpers]
He has a few.
Is he using them to
gather intelligence?
Or are they a part of,
something more?
[NARRATOR]
Just then, Ishida Mitsunari,
Otani Yoshitsugu
and Mori Motonari
paid a visit to
their timid comrade.
[KOBAYAKAWA whimpers] Please,
Mitsunari, just lemme go!
Did you meet with Ieyasu,
or did you not?
Of course not!
That's crazy-talk!
[ISHIDA]
Lie and your life is forfeit!
Okay, I saw him!
Please don't kill me!
Did you agree to betray
Lord Hideyoshi's legacy?
Answer me!
No! Why would I do that?
Ieyasu came to see me
without any invitation!
I'm telling you the truth!
[ISHIDA] I'm disgusted
by the very sight of you!
I'm sorry!
[ISHIDA]
Treachery will be punished!
[KOBAYAKAWA whimpers]
C'mon, I said I was sorry!
[ISHIDA]
Talk to that smiling demon again
and I'll take your head!
[OTANI] And what are your
thoughts on this new wrinkle?
This weakling's
beneath my notice.
Terrorize him as you will.
I ventured here to
see another man.
You should follow suit.
[OTANI]
Hm?
[TENKAI] You have traveled far,
Lord Mori and Master Gyobu.
I am humbled by your attentions.
[MORI]
I would have your name.
What do you gain by
your machinations?
[TENKAI]
Machinations, my lord?
I am but a humble advisor
who tugs at his ear.
Koyabakawa would
never deal in betrayal.
He lacks the guile for it.
[MORI] You expect me to
believe this nonsense?
[TENKAI] I can prove that
our interests are aligned.
[MORI]
Prove it how?
[TENKAI]
Observe, good sirs.
Lady Matsu,
the wife of Maeda Toshiie
of the land of Kaga.
[MORI]
Why is she here?
[TENKAI]
I kidnapped her,
and laid blame for the
abduction at Ieyasu's feet.
What a fine ally her lovelorn
husband will make for us.
[MATSU whimpers]
[OTAN giggles] This stranger's
a man after my own heart.
[MORI]
His methods are brutish.
[TENKAI]
I don't recall either of you
springing to free
her from captivity.
You expect to be
brought into the fold;
that is your insinuation?
[TENKAI] If you honor me thus,
you shall gain much by it.
[OTANI] In that case,
welcome, trickster.
[MORI]
You trust him?
[OTANI] The spear I wield today
may skewer me tomorrow.
He has his uses, Mori.
[MORI]
I hope that you are right.
[OTANI giggles] He fills my
nose with the scent of ruin.
His own, I trust.
[OTANI] We'll be receiving a
guest at Osaka Castle soon.
Let us prepare for them.
[SARUTOBI] You're as
quick as ever, I see.
[KASUGA]
And you're as talkative!
[SARUTOBI]
Sorry to rope you into this.
[KASUGA]
I'm not here for your sake.
My Lord Kenshin
commanded it, that's all.
[SARUTOBI chuckles]
[OTANI]
Show yourself, Takeda monkey.
I've been waiting.
[SARUTOBI]
You're pretty observant.
Guess we'll cut
to the chase, then.
Alliance. You in?
[OTANI] We have no desire to
drag a sickly Tiger about.
But I am perfectly willing to
discuss terms of surrender.
I know we've hit a rough patch,
but, you shouldn't write
off the Takeda just yet.
[OTANI]
It never hurts to be wary.
What say we put your
words to the test?
[BOTH
Huh?
[OTANI]
Mitsunari!
Tokugawa spies have
breached my chamber!
[SARUTOBI]
Son of a--!
[gasps]
[ISHIDA grunts]
[SARUTOBI grunts]
Are you hurt, Gyobu?
[OTANI]
Not in the slightest.
Ieyasu sent you?
You deal with him.
It's your mission!
Oh yeah.
[ISHIDA grunts]
[SARUTOBI grunts]
I won't allow Ieyasu's minions
to stain the sanctity
of Osaka Castle!
[ISHIDA, SARUTOBI grunting]
I could use a
little help here!
You're saying he's
out of your league?
Why aren't you
down here yet?!
[gasps]
[CHOSOKABE yells]
You bilge-rats are in
cahoots with the enemy?
Sorry, but I think you're
on your own over there.
Figured that!
[ISHIDA, SARUTOBI grunting]
Repent your villainy in hell!
[CHOSOKABE chuckles, yells]
[grunts]
[CHOSOKABE]
If y'want fancy,
you're in the wrong
port of call, woman.
[BOTH grunting]
[chuckles]
Cornered, are ya? Well Kasuga,
that didn't take long.
You're a fine one to talk!
[CHOSOKABE yells]
[ISHIDA yells]
[BOTH grunt]
[gasps]
[SARUTOBI]
Up here, guys!
Tricky bastards!
Goin' after an unarmed man!
Why did you come here,
Tokugawa swine?
[SARUTOBI] Look, I'm not
trying to be contrary,
but we're not with Tokugawa.
What?
[OTANI] It's true.
He's Takeda's monkey.
Seems like Otani's the
cleverest chimp in the jungle.
Isn't that right.
Takeda?
No matter!
[SARUTOBI, KASUGA gasp]
All who breach these
walls must pay in blood,
regardless of who they serve!
[OTANI]
Easy, Mitsunari.
[ISHIDA grunts]
[OTANI] The Takeda bear
no love for Tokugawa,
but Ieyasu desires an alliance
with them all the same.
Spare these monkeys' lives,
and forge a pact
with their master.
Deprive Ieyasu of the
comrades he desires.
Say your piece.
My master wishes
to meet you.
As we were telling Otani,
the Takeda want to
partner up with you.
[NARRATOR]
At that moment,
from the far reaches
of the east,
a rival lord's army
sped towards Osaka.
Wait, my lord!
You're not gonna change
my mind, Katakura.
Our current course will
take us straight into lands
under Sanada's protection, sire!
[scoffs]
[DATE] I'll knock him
on his ass if I have to!
[KATAKURA grunts]
Sasuke hasn't returned yet?
I had thought he'd
be back by now.
[TAKEDA SOLDIER 4B]
Commander!
[SANADA]
Yes? Have you word of Sasuke?
No! We're under attack!
Under attack?
[SANADA] Lord Masamune,
what is the meaning of this?
Sanada, this ain't about us.
You an' me'll get
our dance later.
The Tiger's domain is not a
path to be trod by any who ask!
[DATE]
Step aside, kid.
I am one royally pissed
off dragon right now!
[grunts]
[SARUTOBI]
Oh!
This all looks
delightfully awkward.
[gasps]
[DATE]
Ishida.
[SARUTOBI] Hey, it's bad form
pulling something like this
while I'm gone, you know.
Makes you wonder what
our guest's gonna think.
[SANADA]
Master Ishida!
Truly, I'm honored that you
would come all this way!
Fill your hands,
you son of a bitch!
[gasps]
Why should I?
[DATE]
It's been a minute, Ishida.
I was just on my way to see you.
Gotta say, it's decent of
ya to save me the trouble.
I'm gonna pay you back
for happened that day
right here an' now!
[SANADA gasps]
[KATAKURA, SARUTOBI grunt]
And you are, who, again?
[gasps]
[DATE]
Bastard!
Think back to Odawara.
--Odawara?
--[DATE] That's right!
We fought a duel that day!
It was epic, dammit!
That day, my Lord Hideyoshi
was laid low by treachery.
I defeated multitudes.
Not one was worth remembering.
You bore me. Begone, fool.
[gasps]
[grunts]
[DATE yells]
[DATE]
Ishida!
[DATE yells]
[SANADA]
[SANADA, DATE grunting]
Sanada! Get outta my way!
Never!
Master Ishida is a guest
here under my protection!
I would die before I
let harm befall him!
[DATE]
Is that so?
All right.
I'll start this party off
by killing you first!
[NARRATOR]
Next time, "Defeat."