[AYAME] Are you guys ready
for this war to get hardcore?
Yeah, you already
said that last time.
SOX is finally going all
the way, full-tilt to the hilt,
and I for one am
covered in goose bumps!
[AYAME chuckles]
Those Prefects oughta
brace themselves.
Like a bride on
her wedding night.
So, this big, risky idea that
you were telling us about,
what exactly does it entail?
[AYAME]
Good question.
The first thing that we'll need
to put this plan into motion is:
A pair of Tanukichi's
dirty drawers.
[TANUKICHI]
Uh?!
[NARRATOR]
The future. Japan.
For decades, "The Law for
Public Order and Morals
in Healthy Child-Raising"
has banned all sexual content.
This law against libidinous
language, in combination
with the Peacemaker
surveillance technology,
has turned what used
to be an island nation
of anything-goes sexual
deviancy into the country
with the healthiest
public morality on Earth.
But, among the douched masses,
are subversives who would dare
oppose this brave new world
free of naughty thoughts.
This is the story of
these sick miscreants!
[AYAME]
Cock and balls!
[TANUKICHI]
Why is this happening?
The reason why the underwear
thieves keep returning
to Tokioka Academy to steal
our undies is the smell.
[TANUKICHI]
Huh? The smell?
Yeah, because at
this time of year,
teenagers' underpants
get so dank and sweaty
that they produce a
very pungent odor.
So, we'll use these
musty undies as a weapon
to attack Gathered Fabric's
already highly aroused
"down there" organs!
[KOSURI]
Hm.
Down where, exactly?!
Halfway down their faces?!
Please say it's their noses!
Oh, just calm down.
Now then, take a deep breath
for me... and exhale...
...and cum in your pants.
Hey! Don't try to hypnotize me!
All I'm saying is that
we'll use your aromatic,
sweat-soaked boxers as bait
to lure the bandits out.
Oh, man, what am
I doing with my life?
[OTOME]
"Okuma!
Just clear your mind and
focus yourself on my banana."
"Oh, Goriki! My dirty underwear
is touching your banana!"
"Okuma, make my smelly
banana smell even smellier--"
[KOSURI] Hey, Saotome.
Quit babbling to yourself
like a lunatic and get
back to work before I--
[OTOME]
Silence! I'm in the zone!
I must let this genius
pour out of me now!
[panting]
[KOSURI] Sheesh, why am I the
one who's stuck doing this?
All right, in order
to carry out this plan,
we're going to split
up into two teams.
The first team
will hide porno mags
all around the school perimeter.
We'll call them Team Engorged
Clitoris as a codename.
[TANUKICHI] But you're the
only one who can say that!
Oh, fine then, I guess we'll
just call them Team Prong.
Is that better for you?
Like I was saying,
Team Prong's mission
will be to plant dirty
magazines outside Tokioka.
Kosuri and Saotome,
that'll be your position.
Hey, wait, why can't I be
on the same team as you?
[AYAME]
Meanwhile, the other team
is going to penetrate
the school's interior.
And our codename will be
Team Cum Inside, okay?
[TANUKICHI] Again, that
name won't do us any good
if you're the only
one who can say it!
[AYAME] All right,
whatever. Team Tuck-In.
That's gonna be
me and Tanukichi.
I'll dress up as
Blue Snow and scatter
deliciously filthy pictures
throughout the halls
in order to distract
the Prefects.
And while that's going on,
Tanukichi will catch
the underwear thieves.
Besides embarrassing
the Prefects,
we'll also get to show
everybody that SOX
isn't aligned with
Gathered Fabric.
[KOSURI]
Huh?
It sounds like
you'll be taking on
most of the risk
yourself, Ayame.
[AYAME]
Oh, don't worry about me.
Tanukichi's soiled skivvies
will keep me nice and safe.
Well, you'll see what
I mean tomorrow.
[OTOME]
"Okuma!"
"Oh, Goriki! We can't!
Please don't touch me there!"
[KOSURI] Darn it, Team Tuck-In
gets to have all the fun.
It's not right.
By now, I should've already
hijacked Okuma's position
in the SOX hierarchy.
[AYAME]
Listen up, boys!
It's time for you to receive
Blue Snow's divine blessing!
Evening pussy juice,
fresh squeezed!
Drink it all up, boys!
[MALE STUDENTS cheering]
Blue Snow just showed
up outta nowhere.
She's thrown the entire
school into chaos.
Now's the perfect time
to snatch some undies.
Guess it's starting.
[beeping]
Hey, Okuma, where
the heck are you?
[TANUKICHI] Uh, I'm out
patrolling with Kajo.
So, uh, think Blue
Snow's behind this?
[RAIKI]
Absolutely.
As soon as the ruckus
started, I spotted her.
Listen, there's a
ton of disgusting
and indecent material out here.
I need you to come and
help me clean it up!
[TANUKICHI]
Got it!
Wait. What? Kajo?
Uh, sorry, Goriki!
Kajo's chasing after
somebody we suspect
is one of the underwear thieves.
He could be dangerous.
I should help.
[AYAME] As long as my
wings don't fall off,
as long as dicks don't fall off,
as long as we have hearts,
as long as we have pussies,
I can fly anywhere!
[AYAME laughing]
[TANUKICHI]
I feel like such an idiot.
I mean, can I really lure them
here with just my scent?
[gasps]
[TANUKICHI]
There's two of them?
[TANUKICHI] Oh yeah, that's
definitely Gathered Fabric!
I can't believe
they actually came.
[TANUKICHI]
Don't move! Hands in the air!
Huh?
[TANUKICHI]
Anna?!
Mister Okuma.
The sweetest scent
lured me here.
At last you show me that
you're ready to accept my love.
[TANUKICHI]
Uhh...
[ANNA]
You sent me a signal.
A delicious fragrance
that only I can smell.
Uh, I, um, I'm not--
[TANUKICHI screaming]
Oh, I am so... ecstatic.
My love for you is once again
flowing out of me like a geyser!
[ANNA screaming]
[TANUKICHI]
Hey, wait, Miss Tsukimigusa,
Why aren't you stopping this?
Aren't you a Prefect?
Yes, but Mister Matsukage
has instructed me
to prioritize the
desires of Miss Anna
over all other directives.
So ping pong balls and
toilet paper are lewd,
but what she's doing isn't?
--[ANNA yelps]
--[squelches]
[TANUKICHI]
Uh! Get off!
Mister Okuma's voice is
vibrating all throughout my body
and it feels absolutely amazing!
[TANUKICHI] This is all
a big misunderstanding!
I didn't do any of this for you!
It was a trap!
It was just supposed to lure
out the underwear thieves!
[ANNA]
Hm?
So these boxer
shorts weren't a gift
intended to thank me
for all my affection?
Or to signify your willingness
to finally reciprocate
those romantic feelings?
On the contrary...
Oh. That's disappointing.
Yes, well, I still
need some bait
to catch the underwear
thief, so if I could just
--have these back.
--No, I won't give them up!
I've done so much to try
and win your heart.
Don't I deserve some kind
of reward for my efforts?
[sobs]
Oh, come on!
You can't honestly tell me
that that doesn't qualify
as indecent behavior!
Tell her to stop!
I thought I made
myself clear earlier.
I'm required to put Anna's
wishes ahead of everything else.
Mister Matsukage was
explicit about that.
[TANUKICHI] Does logic
even exist on your planet?
[OBORO]
When he gave me this assignment,
Mister Matsukage
stipulated five provisions.
Huh? Like what?
Well, number one,
I must keep secret
any information that
could taint young boys.
As well as any intelligence
gathered by a
government organization.
Number two, entrance
into Anna's bedroom,
bathroom, or any place
she might undress,
is strictly prohibited
at all times.
Number three, while
obeying Provision two,
I am never supposed to
leave Miss Anna's side
whenever obscene acts
are taking place.
Number four, I am to
shield Miss Anna's eyes
from anything lewd
or lascivious.
Number five,
taking numbers one, two, three,
and four into consideration,
ignore them all
if they in any way
conflict with Miss
Anna's desires.
Like the "Three Laws of
Robotics" but effed-up?
[OBORO]
That's not all.
He also told me that I
have to protect Miss Anna
from any lustful acts that
may be inflicted upon her.
However, if she for any reason
wants to initiate such
activities herself,
then I'm not authorized
to stop her.
[TANUKICHI]
In other words,
if Anna wants to poke at
my dick, that's just fine.
But if I were to
grope Anna's melons,
Tsukimigusa would
poke my eyes out?
Well, that hardly seems fair.
[footsteps]
[gasps]
[STUDENT A] Boxers ripe for
the taking? It's our lucky day!
[STUDENT B] Good thing
we followed our noses!
It's Gathered Fabric.
[ANNA] Mister Okuma's intimates.
My precious reward.
They'll pay for this!
Miss Tsukimigusa, let's go
catch those little thieves
and get back my musky undies!
[OBORO]
Yes, ma'am.
[ANNA] Get back here!
Give me back my boxer shorts!
Huh?!
So while I was doing
all kinds of grueling work
for Team Prong and you were
putting yourself in danger,
that loser got his underpants
stolen and failed?
[AYAME]
No.
Tanukichi didn't fail at all.
This is what I wanted.
[KOSURI]
Uh?
[AYAME] As a reward for
a job well done, Tanukichi,
you may boil or grill Saotome's
feet, whichever you prefer.
[OTOME] Hey, how did my name get
dragged into this conversation?
Kosuri's reports made one
thing very clear to me.
You were goofing off out there,
drawing when you
should've been working.
[OTOME] You little snitch!
How dare you rat me out!
[WAITER] I most humbly apologize
for keeping you waiting.
I have one large sugar water
and one "forbidden
switch" for you, ma'am.
[OTOME]
Wait. What is that?
What are you doing?
No, Stop it! Let me go
right now! Unhand me!
[AYAME]
Tickle, tickle, tickle, tickle!
[laughing]
Here. Give it a try, Tanukichi.
I'll pass. So that was
your plan all along?
[AYAME]
Yup!
We'll have Anna
off our tails now.
Yeah, she'll be way
too preoccupied
with that pair of your
dirty crotch-warmers.
[AYAME] Lately, you've caused
Anna's sexual frustration
to reach its peak.
Like a dick that could
rupture at any minute
because it's been a week
since it was jerked off.
[TANUKICHI]
It doesn't "rupture"!
And besides, Anna
doesn't even have one.
I knew if we hung up
your stank undies,
Anna's superhuman senses
would lead her right to them.
But your pheromones
were effective
beyond my wildest dreams!
[TANUKICHI]
What am I, a virgin sacrifice?
[AYAME] That's it.
The foreplay ends here.
Now we go all the way.
So let's talk about
Phase Two of the plan.
Team Prong will again be
in charge of distributing
dirty magazines all around
the school perimeter.
Is that clear, Saotome?
[laughing]
Meanwhile, those of
us on Team Tuck-In,
we're setting the real trap.
And this time we're gonna catch
Gathered Fabric in the act.
We'll leave Saotome's panties
in the middle of the school.
How'd you get those?!
[laughing]
[AYAME] These teddy bear
panties will be the bait
in our bear trap.
I'm counting on you, okay?
Yeah, yeah, I understand.
[AYAME]
Here, take a closer look
so you know what
you're working with.
[KOSURI] So I'm just stuck
being on the outside again?
Why does she trust
that loser so much?
No way!
[AYAME] Listen up, boys! Receive
Blue Snow's divine blessing!
Morning Pussy juice!
[MALE STUDENTS cheering]
[RAIKI]
Resist the urge, boys! Fight it!
[PREFECT A] Don't touch
that filth! Avert your eyes!
Panties. I smell
some panties. Uh.
Jackpot!
[TANUKICHI]
Freeze!
Oh, A fellow snatcher, huh?
[TANUKICHI] Who'd've thought
all those wrestling matches
with Anna would come in handy?
Well, one down.
[OTOME] The other team is having
quite the action-packed day.
[AYAME laughing]
[PREFECTS shouting]
Wait for me!
We got you now!
Why's he hurting
his fellow deviant?
[TANUKICHI] Here's a little
gift for you from SOX!
[PREFECT B]
Hey, wait! Get back here!
[KOSURI] You're the brave
leader who orchestrated
the Tokioka student storming
of Yatsuga Forest, aren't you?
[HYOKA] I have no idea
to what you are referring.
I am currently in the middle
of watching the birds docking.
So, would you kindly leave
me alone, whoever you are.
That's not nice.
And I was about to do you a
colossal favor and tell you
how you could get even more
directly involved with SOX
if only you'd lend me your ears.
Please, just for a second.
[HYOKA] The impeccable
timing of your smile
and that little
tilt of your head,
combined with the way
you clasp your hands
and the sweet squeak
of your voice,
your every mannerism
is deliberately designed
to charm your target.
You must be quite intelligent.
[KOSURI]
Hmph.
Wow, you're even more
hardcore than I expected.
To be able to size
me up that quickly?
[HYOKA]
So who do you work for?
[KOSURI]
I am an official member of SOX.
In order to get relief
from all of the tension
that society imposes on us,
I'd suggest you take
action right away.
[TANUKICHI]
All right, that's ten down.
Although,
seems like things are going
a little too smoothly.
Why was it so easy for
me to catch this many?
[alarm blaring]
[TANUKICHI]
Is it a fire? What's happening?
[door opens]
[TANUKICHI]
Crap! More Gathered Fabric?
So be it!
Enjoy my father's ultra-lethal
uber-secret move.
[TANUKICHI]
Electric Massage!
Look, don't blame me.
It's your own fault
for being so stubborn.
Uh?
Is that... Tsukimigusa?
What the heck's going on here?
What does it... look like...?
[TANUKICHI]
So, you're a dude?
Yes. That is correct.
[TANUKICHI] Then why were
you pretending to be a girl?
[OBORO] Another of
Mister Matsukage's orders.
He thought my mission would
go more smoothly this way
and that as a girl,
I'd be able to enter both
male and female spaces
and better suppress vulgarity.
And, of course, it's
possible he was also thinking
that if I disguised
myself as a girl,
then maybe Miss Anna wouldn't
be in quite so much danger.
[TANUKICHI]
She was in danger?
[OBORO]
es.
If I were ever to behave
like a boy around her,
there was a danger that I would
develop impure feelings for her
and potentially
even act on them.
[TANUKICHI] But that means
you have no real identity
of your own.
[OBORO]
I do have an identity.
If Mister Matsukage tells
me to be male, I'm male.
If he tells me to be
female, I'm female.
If Miss Anna thinks
peppers are delicious,
then I think they're delicious.
If she says pudding
is disgusting,
then I say it's disgusting.
That is my identity.
Mister Matsukage said it
would be for the best this way.
[TANUKICHI]
Oh, god.
[knocking]
Miss Tsukimigusa, have
you finished changing?
[TANUKICHI] Wait, what are
you doing in here anyway?
[OBORO] Well, while
Miss Anna was engrossed
in your undergarments, the
sprinklers suddenly went off,
so I rushed in here to
change out of my wet clothes
before they became see-through.
[ANNA] Miss Tsukimigusa?
Are you in there? Can I come in?
[OBORO] I see no reason
why not, Miss Anna.
[TANUKICHI gasps]
[ANNA] Well, you certainly took
your sweet time answeri-- Uh!
It's you! The Mister
Okuma look-alike!
[screams]
[TANUKICHI]
Now!
[ANNA] Oh, even though
you're just a pale imitation,
these smell exactly like him!
Such a yummy aroma!
[AYAME]
Ugh, not again.
You really think you can
appeal to my rotten heart
with some far-fetched lie about
Tsukimigusa being a boy?
[TANUKICHI] Uh, but I'm
telling you the truth.
Go and check for yourself
and you'll see I'm right.
[siren wailing]
[AYAME]
Can't now. The firemen are here.
We'll have to abort the rest
of our operations for today.
[KOSURI laughs]
Glad I caught you both.
[AYAME] Kosuri? Why are you
dressed up like that?
And what are you doing here?
[chuckles]
Ha! Well, I scored a major
victory for SOX's mission today,
so you're all very welcome.
I personally approached Fuwa,
the ringleader of
the normal students,
and managed to get her to commit
to helping out my brother.
I told her to send
any Gathered Fabrics
that she came across
to the changing room
where Brother would
be waiting for them.
[TANUKICHI]
What happened?
[KOSURI] Well, see, I also
asked her to slow down
and obstruct the Prefects
in whatever way she could,
but she refused to cooperate
with me on that one.
So, I had to take matters
into my own hands
and get them all soaking wet
by squirting them myself.
Phew! Phew!
That was you?
What's wrong?
You jealous 'cause I'm more
useful to SOX than you ever were
and I'm starting to thrust you
out of the number two position?
--[TANUKICHI] Why, you litt--
--[OTOME] This is pointless.
Do you realize the extent
of what you've done
and all the damage
you've caused?
[AYAME]
She's right.
Now let's clear our heads
so we can think of a solution.
Commence masturbation.
I don't get it.
What's the problem?
Kosuri worked hard to win
your approval, Ayame!
I thought you'd be ecstatic!
Issuing orders to Hyoka Fuwa
gives people the impression
that SOX is guiding
ordinary students,
which is an image we'd
rather not have out there.
And setting off the sprinklers
was definitely a bad move.
We gain absolutely
nothing for our cause
by directly attacking the
Establishment like that.
In fact, we lose.
Kosuri was only
trying to help SOX
by sticking it to
our repressive enemies
and give them
what they deserve.
[AYAME]
What we aim to do here
is not to destroy the Decency
Squad or to injure the Prefects.
And we're not looking to slander
the Student Council, either.
Those aren't the peaceful
forms of protest
we embrace here at SOX.
[KOSURI]
What's wrong with you people?
Rhetorical BS?
Pandering to the Establishment?
These guys are no different
than my decrepit old father.
Pardon me. I've brought--
[AYAME] Ooh, what is that?
Hot towel service?
I'm afraid it's not a hot towel.
Someone tossed that into
the restaurant, ma'am.
This is--
[WHITE PEAK] I'm pleased to
see that the members of SOX
made it out tonight.
I am the leader
of Gathered Fabric.
Call me White Peak.
[TANUKICHI] Next episode:
"Masturbation Quest."