[WHITE PEAK] I'm pleased to
see that the members of SOX
made it out tonight.
I'm leader of the resistance
group, Gathered Fabric.
Call me White Peak.
[AYAME]
I am the leader of SOX.
And if this city were a
pure white butt cheek,
I'd be its beauty mark.
I am Blue Snow!
[chuckles]
I hope this little
diplomatic summit
proves beneficial to both
of our organizations.
[KOSURI]
Um, did something slip out?
[OTOME] I must say,
the size, shape, and color
are completely different than
anything else I've ever seen.
[TANUKICHI]
Listen to me, Blue Snow.
This guy's a total freak show.
We can't negotiate with him.
Oh, for shame.
How can my dink
dangling bother you?
If anything, I should
be disappointed in SOX.
To think, all those
panties on your heads...
...are clean and free of odor!
You prudes!
[TANUKICHI]
Of course, they're clean!
You think you're perverts?
You should know
a panty's true worth
is in its former user's aroma!
White ones, in particular,
are highly regarded
as the most desirable.
[AYAME chuckles]
[AYAME] That may be true,
but let me ask you this.
Do you think those stink
briefs you're wearing
are really helping you?
That rank smell will
eventually make you sick.
[WHITE PEAK]
Uh.
It would seem that
you're calling me out.
True. I've worn these
panties for so long
I've not only forgotten
their original owner
their scent has gone
from a pleasant musk
to that of a bucket
of rotting oysters.
[TANUKICHI]
Gross.
I must smell some new,
used panties on my face.
It's this hunger that
gives Gathered Fabric
its mission on Earth! Panties!
[AYAME]
You're no dirty joke terrorist
trying to bring
about social change.
You just formed this
group to help you steal
soiled undies for your fetish!
Ha! Are you so desperate
to be seen as legitimate
that you guys look down on me?
I guess tonight's diplomatic
summit has been a failure.
You have no plans
to cease your hunting
of my Gathered Fabric
goons, do you?
[AYAME]
Of course not. We'll never stop.
We're like a 13-year-old
boy who just learned
how to white wall his shower.
Then you leave me no choice.
I shall do whatever it takes
to guarantee my pleasure.
I'll gladly hurt the innocent.
Destroy the whole world!
Make it drown in a
sea of soiled panties!
You children will never
stop our terrorism!
[WHITE PEAK laughing]
Do you get it, Kosuri?
Like a working girl's
jaw, he's unhinged.
[KOSURI] Oh, I get it.
What a horrible organization.
And now,
I got a feeling in my gut
they're planning a big attack.
Something that makes
their usual panty raids
seem like family fun.
But whatever it is,
we'll be there to stop it.
[NARRATOR]
The future. Japan.
For decades, "The Law for
Public Order and Morals
in Healthy Child-Raising"
has banned all sexual content.
This law against libidinous
language, in combination
with the Peacemaker
surveillance technology,
has turned what used
to be an island nation
of anything-goes sexual
deviancy into the country
with the healthiest
public morality on Earth.
But, among the douched masses,
are subversives who would dare
oppose this brave new world
free of naughty thoughts.
This is the story of
these sick miscreants!
[AYAME]
Cock and balls!
[KOSURI] Have a good day
at school, Big Brother!
Why take the train if it's
just gonna break down?
Yeah, now I'm late
for an interview.
C'mon, let's move!
Oh, man. That was too close.
[RAIKI]
Morning, Okuma!
[gasps]
[TANUKICHI]
Goriki?
--[COMMUTER E] Wait for me!
--[COMMUTER D] No!
Are you flustered because the
monorail is mysteriously broken
and we're all being
forced to take the bus?
Yeah, I guess so.
But bus or train, I think I was
gonna be late no matter what.
At least the buses are
roomy and reasonably clean.
But that train
problem worries me.
Maybe someone cut the power
to the remote traffic system?
It's too big to be a prank.
So, you think it was a crime?
Yeah. And just when
things were looking up
with the decline
in underwear theft.
I just hope this isn't the work
of some depraved
terrorist group.
White Peak?
[beeping]
[AYAME]
Tanukichi,
please tell me you are not
riding on a bus right now.
Uh...
[COMMUTERS screaming]
[TERRORIST A]
Everybody, stay calm!
This bus is being hijacked
by Gathered Fabric!
[COMMUTER D gasps]
[COMMUTER C screams]
So, uh, hey, Kajo?
I'm gonna have to hang up
because I'm being bus-jacked.
[ANCHOR A] We interrupt the
"Yakking Yoga" after-show
with breaking news.
A bus has been hijacked by the
panty-stealing terrorist group
that calls itself Gathered
Fabric. Authorities...
Oh, no. Now they've
really done it.
Oh. Then I must've
been bus-jacked.
This is an impressive attack
for Gathered Fabric.
Miss Tsukimigusa,
I don't want you to make
any moves without my say so.
Yes, I understand.
Now I see.
This's what he meant by
"doing whatever it takes."
[SQUAD BOSS A]
Status report!
How many bus jackings
are we talking about?
[UNDERLING A] Sir,
intelligence reports 42 buses
hijacked by men and women
with panties on their heads.
Well, how hard can it
be to take them back?
These aren't terrorists,
they're fetishists.
But, sir, the bus
jackers are carrying
military grade,
automatic weapons.
[static]
Hello there, Decency Squad.
I am leader of the group
that's stolen your buses.
You can call me, White Peak.
My god!
Now he's hijacked our
communication systems!
Gathered Fabric is in
full alliance with SOX.
Our shared goal is to
make Japan weird again.
So we all have
the right to enjoy
the musk of panties
worn by other crotches.
And for this freedom we
will go to war with you!
Well, That's a very
odd mission statement.
[TERRORIST B] Hey, dark eyes,
what are you musing about?
I'm only watching the news.
Well, pay attention to me.
I'm pointing an Uzi at you.
[HYOKA]
Your conviction impresses me.
May I ask you
about your beliefs?
What is it about panties,
items that play no
role in reproduction,
that arouse such erotic
passions in some people?
I've had just about
enough of your babbling.
Don't make me shoot you!
How are you going to
shoot me with a fake gun?
I've observed the
tension in your hand
and compared it to the
usual weight of that gun.
Your grip is far too loose.
When combined with the fact that
the plastic inside the barrel
is clearly visible, I can
conclude beyond a doubt
that this is a toy.
So I ask you again,
what is it about underwear
fabric that you love?
Does it give you
the sensual thrill
that others get from
graphic pictures?
I appreciate any answer you can
provide, however simplistic.
Uh, look, either you
get it or you don't, kid.
It's about way more
than just fabric.
Now listen, you're gonna
take off your pan-- Ah!
Hey, what are you doing?!
You're hijacking my hijacking!
Oh, wow. This thing
is just a toy!
Hey, thanks, kid.
Oh, uh, I didn't really--
[COMMUTER I]
Thanks, Miss.
Yeah, you noticed her fake gun.
And then you started
getting in her head,
playing the mind games.
Did I? But, sir, I am
but a humble scientist.
I was merely trying to
gather more information.
[OBORO]
Miss Anna, ae you okay?
You've been muttering
uncontrollably
for the last few minutes.
Yeah. It's not fear I'm
fighting, it's withdrawal.
You see, I've gone...
too long...
...without being able to touch
Mister Okuma's underpants.
I couldn't even find a
pair at his apartment.
It's been a week since his
musk has filled my nostrils.
If I don't smell
his undies soon,
I won't be able to stop shaking.
I had no idea.
[TERRORIST B]
Hey, you two!
No more talking.
I will now collect
your undergarments.
Both tops and bottoms.
The dirtier, the better.
Hey, this isn't
a request, people.
Now drop those pants
and hike those skirts.
If I don't see some crotches,
you're gonna see some lead.
Mister Okuma's
always teasing me.
Why won't he stop
playing hard to get?
In there.
My love.
His coldness must mean
my actions are still
lacking in righteousness.
Come on.
And If my actions
aren't righteous,
he won't fall in love with me.
'Kay. Take 'em off, ladies.
Oh, wait.
This might be my chance
to do something righteous.
Hey! I said take 'em off!
I'll shoot--
[ANNA] Lewdness.
I won't allow it. Be gone!
Lewdness be gone!
Be gone!
[TERRORIST B screaming]
That was great, Miss Anna.
[giggles]
Now that I've defeated
this horrible man,
I know Mister Okuma will fall
in love with me for real.
Man, these guys
are so perverted.
[TERRORIST A]
Hey, you, Gorilla.
[RAIKI]
Hm?
Let's see that underwear!
[RAIKI]
Uh...
Easy, Goriki.
We don't wanna make the
situation worse than it is.
My little sister's
gonna be mad at me.
[TERRORIST A sniffing]
Hey. Are you carrying a load
of dirty undies in that bag?
What? No, that's crazy.
[TERRORIST A]
Give 'em!
[chuckles]
When it comes to undies, only
White Peak's nose is better.
Wait, all I smell
in this pile is... you!
Hey, why do you have
a bag of your undies?
Well, it's the only way
I can keep this crazy girl who
likes me from stealing them.
Wait, that sounds weird.
In my family, it's a tradition
that brings good health!
Nothing helps calm the spirit
like one's own scent, right?
Sometimes, on my
lunch break, I'll put a nice,
ripe pair of boxer briefs on my
head and meditate for hours.
[TANUKICHI chuckles]
Okay.
I don't mean to be rude, but
you're not right in the head.
You remind me of
our glorious leader
when he was a younger man.
[TANUKICHI] I'm not taking
that as a compliment.
He's right. You can
be weird, Okuma.
But don't worry.
Your secret is safe.
I accept you for who you are.
Like you accept me.
Thank you. I appreciate
your support.
[retches]
What's wrong, kid?
Are you carsick?
Huh?
[TERRORIST A retches]
Now's our chance!
[COMMUTERS gasp, retch]
What? What's wrong?
Is it Flu season?
[BUS DRIVER]
Huh?
[retches]
[AYAME] Good work escaping
from that bus, Tanukichi.
Though, in the future,
I'd appreciate you using
a more exciting bodily fluid
than vomit.
[TANUKICHI]
Yeah, yeah.
I'm done with
biological warfare.
Still, SOX got
the win. Good boy.
I'm not your pet!
[AYAME] Anyway, I feel like
we're running out of time.
Like a boy who falls
asleep during an assembly
and wakes up with
a boner so strong
it's poking out above
his waistband for air.
Only the assembly's just ended
and the teacher's yelling,
"All right, everybody! Time to
get up and get back to class."
[TANUKICHI]
Ayame,
I'm not sure these analogies of
yours are really that helpful.
What?
If you take your
dick and slide it,
so it's as close as possible
to your belt buckle,
the cold from the metal
should shrink it.
With that, your tent is down.
Now that's helpful.
Can we please have
a conversation
without you saying
something nasty?
With one move, White Peak
put us in check today.
Gathered Fabric
hijacked your bus,
while you and Goriki
were busy laughing it up
over your disgusting fetishes.
We were not!
Anyway, White Peak addressed
the Feds and mentioned SOX,
thereby making us all
guilty by association.
If they arrest Gathered Fabric,
we won't be far behind.
We're ruined if we're
lumped in with them.
Whadda we do now?
[AYAME]
The only thing we can do.
We're getting the team together
and SOX will catch
White Peak ourselves
to prove we're not the same.
You're serious?
[AYAME]
It's the only way.
The D.S. knows his real name.
You missed that news, 'cause
you were getting hijacked,
and probably busy
flirting with Goriki again
over your shared love
for ladies' undergarments
and god knows what else.
That never happened!
Takuma Ichinose,
that's his real name.
He's in his last year at school.
Well, if they know that much,
I bet he's being
arrested as we speak.
No.
Ichninose is still out there,
moving from bus to bus.
Which means we have a
chance to get him first.
[NEWS ANCHOR B] Breaking
news in the terror attacks
that have paralyzed a city!
The Decency Squad has stated
that 39 buses remain hijacked
by the organization calling
itself Gathered Fabric.
Authorities are urging
citizens to avoid the roads...
He's moving so fast.
At this point, it's impossible
for us to catch up.
Yeah, yeah, you're
such a negative Nancy.
You gotta relax. Breathe
in and breathe out...
--...and cum.
--I won't!
[AYAME]
You can't?
[TANUKICHI]
That's not what I said!
Don't get bent out of shape.
It's nothing a psychiatrist
and some pills can't fix.
Thanks for your concern.
Let's get back to
the task at hand.
All right.
Of the 42 buses, Gathered
Fabric still has 39.
Including the bus you
and Goriki were on,
passengers successfully defended
their underwear on three buses.
Others fought back?
One hostage who freed herself
was a girl with dark
circles under her eyes.
Another, was a girl
with a bob of silver hair.
Huh. Really is a small world
when you get down to it.
White Peak admitted
to the Decency Squad
that with the exception of
one bus hijacker's weapon,
all the firearms they were
carrying were stage props.
So to determine who's
got the real gun,
the Decency Squad's getting
help from our friend, Hyoka,
the girl with dark
circles under her eyes.
[TANUKICHI] Yeah, but that
still means we're outta time,
'cause the second they
find the real gun,
they'll rush the other buses
and round up the hijackers.
Not true. The police
are very risk averse.
If they go in on Hyoka's word
alone, and a hostage dies,
they'll be in trouble.
They won't move till
they're certain.
But still.
If they're watching
every bus now,
how are we supposed to not only
get on the one Ichinose is on,
but then get him off it?
We'll lure his bus
to a narrow street
where the cops can't drive
their truck to the side.
Then, with the Decency Squad
unable to see what's happening,
we'll jump on, grab that
jerk, and get out quick.
And then, after
alerting the government
that SOX has
kidnapped White Peak,
we'll go into hiding
with him as our hostage.
That sounds insane.
How are we even gonna find
the bus Ichinose is on,
let alone take him hostage?
Oh, we can find his bus.
We just need the right bait.
What bait?
So, that's what's going on.
And now we really need
your help. Are you in?
[KOSURI]
Of course!
Kosuri can get everything
we need for this awesome plan.
It's going to be great!
I love it!
Look out White Peak!
We're coming for you!
[TANUKICHI]
Take this seriously!
I smell a unique
pair of panties.
[AYAME]
I have a visual.
The panty scent's effective
within a 500 meter radius.
Now find a narrow road
we can lure him onto
using the rest of the panties
that Kosuri collected.
[AYAME screams]
What was that? Kajo?
[AYAME] I'm fine! Just hurry
up and find us that road!
Found one. Four miles north.
A mountain access road that
cuts through Shinrin Square.
[AYAME]
Spank you!
[TANUKICHI]
Be serious!
Look, Kajo, I'm heading
toward you right now.
Please don't do anything crazy.
A Blue Snow sighting?
But we already have
our hands full
with all the day's jackings.
But think. It seems Blue Snow
is using panties like a flare,
trying to guide Takuma
Ichinose somewhere else.
So what if we could
use that method, too?
Underwear as bait?
I get it now.
What a brilliant plan!
Agreed, but we
need good panties.
Call all female Decency Squad
members in for back up.
What?!
What's wrong?
There's not a single
girl here today
who's wearing white panties.
No.
According to this,
five black pairs,
three red pairs, three
pairs of large Spanx,
and one pink pair of crotchless.
Oh, and two aren't wearing any.
That's enough!
[TANUKICHI]
That's him.
[COP A]
What's going on?
[TANUKICHI]
Now!
[whimpers]
[TANUKICHI]
Close the door! Quick!
Well done, SOX.
You gathered a large amount
of underwear for me
in a short amount of time.
I knew you were trying
to lure me into a trap,
but I couldn't resist
following my nose.
[TANUKICHI]
Put down the gun. It's over.
[WHITE PEAK chuckles]
Are you acting so cocky because
you think this weapon is a fake?
[TANUKICHI] Even if it is real,
there's no way you'll shoot me.
You wanna know why?
Before they were on my mouth,
a real girls' pussy was soaking
these with its musty magic.
These well-worn panties
make me more powerful
than you can possibly imagine!
[COMMUTERS gasping]
Heh. My nose is
well ahead of you.
The panties you've lured me
with make me stronger, not you!
[BOTH gasp]
He is risen!
You misguided fool!
What you thought was
my greatest weakness,
has come all the way around
to stab you in the backside!
I only wish Blue Snow were here
to watch her plan
fail so miserably.
I guess she's just
a selfish bitch
who was willing to
sacrifice her own comrade
while she hides like a coward.
[TANUKICHI]
Call her that to my face!
What's that?
You want another punch?
[TANUKICHI]
She's no coward.
And she's certainly
not a moron like you.
Ha! Look.
I've thoroughly defeated you.
Now, take these off
and reveal yourself.
[glass shattering]
[AYAME]
Wait a sex!
So you've come, Blue Snow.
[AYAME] Well, I hope to cum.
I'm tired of this foreplay!
Heh. You really think this
turns the tables on me?
[sniffing]
I don't smell anyone
else with you.
In other words, the panties on
your head are springtime fresh.
And nothing frustrates me more,
than panties without a musk.
These won't stop you
from getting shot.
[WHITE PEAK]
Huh?
Wait.
I do smell... What's going
on with that pair?
[AYAME] True, I may not be
wearing someone else's panties,
as you prefer, but these
are dirty with my stink!
It can't be.
Breathing through panties
infused with your own scent?
You're even crazier than I am!
[AYAME]
Well, well. It's a fake.
I think we know
who the coward is.
White Peak, real name
Takuma Ichinose,
do you know what
your fatal flaw is?
For future reference,
I'll hear you out.
[AYAME] You think that
panties are only of value
if they've been worn
by someone else.
Never once has it dawned on you
to wear your own soiled
underwear on your head.
You're smart, but you let
the nose on your face,
and the trunk between your legs,
lead you rather than the best
erotic organ: Your brain.
And that's no way to live.
Heh. We're just not a match.
[TANUKICHI]
Sorry, Blue Snow.
I didn't mean to get
beat up so easily.
[AYAME]
Eh, it's fine.
Besides, you getting roughed
up is never a bad thing.
Anyway, let's go
talk to the Po-Po.
I am the leader of SOX!
We've captured Takuma Ichinose!
Let's go to a neutral
location to negotiate!
Kindly move your police
vehicles out of the way
so we can get back on the road.
[TANUKICHI]
Watch out!
[AYAME]
Huh?
[AYAME yelps]
[gasps]
[groaning]
[AYAME]
What was that?!
[COP A]
Blue Snow's out of the bus.
[COP B]
Get her!
[TANUKICHI]
Why did you...? How did you...?
When the bus doors opened
and you jumped on to
fight with White Peak,
I came in the back,
dressed as a hostage.
See, I've realized
how pathetic SOX is.
Gathered Fabric's far more
serious about waging war
on our puritanical
society than you are.
It gives me chills.
Mister White Peak,
nice to meet you.
Will you please let Kosuri
join your terrorist group?
I've made plenty of arrangements
for us to have lots of fun.
[TANUKICHI]
Kosuri, no. Don't do this to us.
[KOSURI]
Cram it, "Big Brother."
I'm done with you
limp-noodle clowns.
There'll be consequences if
you don't get out of my sight.
[TANUKICHI]
Next episode: "Techno Break."