[AYAME] Can you believe
you ended up in the hospital
after defending the honor
of the girl you love?
That's basically the situation
every boy dreams of.
"The only way I can thank
you for saving my life
is to bend over and
let you take a bite
out of my tight, round apple.
There's one big seed
deep in that fruit
that I need you to get
out with your tongue."
[RAIKI]
There.
Spread out just for you.
I like Home Ec.
[NARRATOR]
The future. Japan.
For decades, "The Law for
Public Order and Morals
in Healthy Child-Raising"
has banned all sexual content.
This law against libidinous
language, in combination
with the Peacemaker
surveillance technology,
has turned what used
to be an island nation
of anything-goes sexual
deviancy into the country
with the healthiest
public morality on Earth.
But, among the douched masses,
are subversives who would dare
oppose this brave new world
free of naughty thoughts.
This is the story of
these sick miscreants!
[AYAME]
Cock and balls!
[HYOKA] I believe an apple
was the forbidden fruit
that tempted Adam and Eve,
although technically the Bible's
vague on this exact detail. Oof!
What? Hyoka! Why're you here!
A strange question.
To see how you're recuperating,
isn't that obvious?
Then why not come through
the door like a normal person?
I'm afraid that's an
entrance I can't come in.
All the hospitals, labs,
and lab supply houses
in the tri-prefecture area
have blacklisted me.
Wait, so it's not just
the gynecologists?
I had to give you this.
What is it?
A special present.
I trust that he'll live a
long life under your care.
But I'm perplexed.
I thought Mister Goriki
was of the belief
you were lower than pond scum.
But now he's cutting your fruit
into delicate bite-sized pieces.
It's quite unusual.
Side question:
Can babies be created by one man
thrusting his meat pickle into
another man's exhaust passage?
Why would you ask me something
like that while I'm eating?
[HYOKA]
I have my reasons.
Goriki's new
feelings towards you
have me questioning
all my assumptions
about what constitutes "normal"
bodymelding. I'm very confused.
Well, it's not
about meat pickles.
Since I saved Anna
from those stalkers,
he's just finally realized
I'm on his side, is all.
[HYOKA] We'll return to the
question of man love later.
For now, I'd like
to focus on waiting
for the council
President to arrive,
so that I may discuss with her
a most pertinent matter.
[TANUKICHI groans]
Have I struck a nerve?
[TANUKICHI]
Anna doesn't come here.
She hasn't even visited me once.
How rude.
What about a "Thank You" card?
You were injured
protecting her honor.
[TANUKICHI]
Even though it was an accident,
I'm pretty sure she's mad
at me for kissing her.
The only explanation
I can think of
is that she hates
you, Tanukichi.
Stop it! Stop shoving
reality in my face!
Wait, did you say you also came
here hoping to find Anna?
Yes.
The Student Council's crackdown
on inappropriate culture
has ratcheted up in intensity.
Unlawful detentions.
Surprise locker inspections.
Teacher-administered
body cavity searches.
You're positive this is
all on Anna's orders?
Anna's entire life
has been driven
by a burning desire to suppress
all forms of lewdness.
But this is the first time
I've ever observed her
to be so forceful.
That's why I was hoping to
intercept and probe her here
to learn why this desire's
grown even hotter, lately.
Smut in the school. Takes
more than that to stop me.
[OTOME breathing heavily]
I went ahead and told
Saotome the truth about me.
It really got her
juices flowing.
I'm surprised she's
come around so quickly.
It wasn't long ago she
was trying to kill you.
[AYAME]
I know! Now we're best buds.
Saving Anna must've
made her realize
that we're on the same side.
But, wait, if you've got her
drawing dirty pictures for you
while she's wearing her PM,
won't she get arrested?
[AYAME] The PM bracelets only
track hand movements.
There are other ways the girl
can hold a shaft, Tanukichi.
She could draw with her feet,
or she could just stick
the pencil up her hoo-ha.
How far are you
gonna have her go!
Well, that's pretty advanced
stuff and will take some time.
For now, I'm getting her
up to speed on the basics,
hopefully learning about
sex will snap her out of
her creative slump, molding
her into the dirtiest artist
the world's ever
rubbed it out to!
Although...
[OTOME groaning]
No good!
I need live subjects!
I am only able to draw things
I see before my own eyes!
Show me a real example
of physical love!
[TANUKICHI] Anna never came
to visit me even once.
Come on, it's not so bad.
After all, I have come
here to visit you.
But I thought you
were bringing Ayame.
Ayame says she's
booked this afternoon.
Something about having to meet
with another terror group
to do some networking.
SOX isn't the only terror group?
So it would seem. That's all I
really know about the subject.
Is it just me or are
you actually happy?
Yes, it's because
I'm getting close
to breaking out of
my creative slump!
So, I guess being around
Ayame's paying off, huh?
No, I owe it all to Anna.
Wait, Anna?
That's right.
Anna insisted I come up with
some way she could thank me.
So in our spare time,
I have been drawing full
body sketches of her
in various erotic poses!
Wait a second, detailed
full body sketches?
You mean, she's na-na-naked?!
[gasps]
Oh my god, is the reason
Anna never came to visit me
because you've had her tied up
in some twisted art dungeon?
That's not why.
Out of curiosity, I did ask
her why she hasn't come.
Anna, are you sure you need not
visit Okuma in the hospital?
I shall not.
[OTOME] I'd never seen
such a cold-blooded look
on her face before.
It gave me goose bumps.
She hates me now.
My sweet angel won't forgive
me for that one mistaken kiss.
[OTOME]
On the bright side,
Anna's alpha-lady
gravitas on full display
really enlivened my pen!
Then, when I factor in
all of the dirty knowledge
that Ayame has bestowed upon me,
I get the sensation that
a huge creative gusher
is boiling up inside.
I am so close to revelation!
[ANNA]
Next week is the big conference,
the one about the proposed
X Prohibition law.
My mother, Sophia Nishikinomiya,
will be giving a speech...
[TANUKICHI] She hasn't said
a word since I got back.
She won't even look at me.
I was right. She thinks
I'm a total creep.
[RAIKI]
Hey, Okuma.
Tanukichi!
What's up?
You okay? Ya seem tired.
You just got back.
Go home and rest up.
We need you to be
strong and firm.
Oh. Yeah, sorry.
Ayame never made it to
school today, did she?
[RAIKI]
No.
She said she had to take off
for a couple important errands.
As if what we do isn't
important. The nerve.
[BOTH gasp]
[TANUKICHI]
And the avoiding continues.
[gasps]
Who's there?
[beeping]
[AYAME]
Throbbing news, Tanukichi.
--Yeah, what is it?
--[AYAME] It's too big
to tell you on the phone.
Gotta tell it to you in person.
So put your lotion away,
pull up your pants,
and meet at the coffee shop
in 20, 'kay? Cock-suck!
Hey, wait!
[AYAME] Tanukichi! Hey, Buddy,
glad you're feeling better!
I'm feeling great!
I'm as excited as a
middle age house-wife
sitting on a washing machine
during the spin cycle!
All right. I get it.
What's wrong, Tanukichi?
Why so flaccid?
He's probably depressed because
Anna's been ignoring him.
Tanukichi, is it possible
you did something to her
when you had her on the ground?
Maybe you unknowingly
twiddled her nips or pressed
your crotch against hers?
Of course not!
Just tell me what's so important
I have to come to the diner
in the middle of the night.
So grand is my surprise,
it shall make your dick rise!
[TANUKICHI] Can't you just talk
like a normal human being?
Behold!
I've learned of a secret
deep in Yatsuga Forest.
A treasure trove of
erotic literature,
featuring sex scenes so
hardcore, you won't be able to
get up from the couch
because you'll be stuck to it!
Seriously?
I thought the government
had destroyed
all of the unhealthy media that
included scenes of docking.
This erotica is so old,
it falls into kind of
a legal "gray area."
There's every genre, from
romance to rough stuff,
school girls to MILFS,
small boobs to big boobs,
S and M, anal, handjobs,
homoeroticism,
hermaphrodites, tentacle play.
It's a treasure trove
of perversions!
Okay, let's says you
find this porn gusher,
drill it dry and cart it off.
Won't the Decency
Squad find out?
And if the stash is
as big as you say,
how can you be sure they haven't
already found it and burned it?
[chuckles]
All good points,
but this case has a few
special circumstances.
And those would be...?
[AYAME] Yatsuga Forest, my
friends, is private property.
Years ago, it was owned by
the author, Danroku Onigashira
He got rich off
vampire bondage stories.
Anyway, he accidentally
starved to death
in his real life sex dungeon,
so now it's in a trust,
run by his grandson, Keisuke,
who recently found his
grandpa's original will.
This will laid out
specific instructions
for the erotica collection,
which Keisuke was
happy to follow.
These included using the books
to supply the various dirty
joke terrorist organizations.
By now, Keisuke should've
divided the smut evenly
between all the
different groups.
But somehow, word of this
got out to the government,
and when they came
tromping onto the property,
Keisuke had to scramble.
He made up some story
about the land being a private
sanctuary for a rare plant.
"If you trample the
forest's undergrowth,
you'll ruin the matsutake
mushroom harvest this fall."
Such a clever man.
My ears are bleeding.
Know what I'd say
if it was me, though?
"If you steal my porn,
my crotch-mushrooms
will shrivel up and die!"
That's snappier, right?
Yeah, if you wanted
to get arrested!
Back to the story, the search
is delayed three weeks.
In the meantime, the
Decency Squad's beefed up
their surveillance
of the Forest
to the point a single sperm
couldn't get in there.
So, what does all
of that mean for us?
It means in three
weeks we go to war!
In three weeks the forest
will be free from tyranny!
Now if he opts to give up the
stash, obviously we won't go in.
But if he doesn't,
then you're going in the same
time as the decency squad.
That's right. And
terror groups like SOX
are no match for the
government on our own.
We're outnumbered. They'd
easily round us up for arrest.
And those of us
with prior records
will receive severe sentences.
But there's a... but!
[BOTH]
Uh?
What if there were students,
with no experience in joke
terrorism, virgins, okay?
But virgins who nevertheless
had an interest in the craft
of dirty jokes and thoughts.
And what if they were to storm
the forest in such numbers,
they overwhelmed the Decency
Squad three weeks from today,
and they recovered the
erotic books instead.
Unless I'm mishearing
things, it sounds like
you wanna use innocent Tokioka
students as cannon fodder.
Whoa, whoa, whoa, wait.
Stop the clock, Ayame.
We can't do that.
I think we can.
But first, we need
to light the fuses
of their subconscious
curiosity for adventure.
For the next three weeks,
we'll convince the school
there's treasure to be
found in Yatsuga Forest!
Uh?
[AYAME] So, were you
able to hide that stack
of Yatsuga Forest
maps around school?
Has the seed been planted in
their fertile minds, Tanukichi?
[TANUKICHI]
Um. Well, no.
And why not? I better not
find them in a dumpster.
I ordered you to
get them out there
before Anna's mom's
big speech today.
Yeah, I know, but...
I don't think it's a good idea
for me to be sneaking
around like that right now.
[AYAME]
Hm?
All these letters.
So I guess this means
you have a stalker, too.
Here's the most recent one
I found on my desk this morning.
[gasps]
What is this?
Makes Anna's stalkers look
like old-fashioned romantics.
So gross.
So what do I do?
Since the creep factor on
this is through the roof,
I'd lay low.
Besides, the Decency Squad
will be here soon anyway.
[TANUKICHI] What's with
all the armed guards?
[AYAME] Sophia's speech
isn't just for us.
It's being simulcast to
educators around the country
at all the top-ranked
morality schools.
[applause]
So that's Sophia
Nishikinomiya, huh?
Anna's mom.
Japan likes to boast
that we are the undisputed
worldwide leader
in public health and
morally clean living.
But is that really true?
What if the Law for Public
Morals and Healthy Child-Raising
was not nearly as
effective as we all think?
You kids remain
psychologically immature.
More than ever,
your heads are filled
with dirty thoughts
and bad language
that leave you unable to control
your emotions and actions.
We adults have a duty
to guide you all
to a higher moral ground.
That is why I'm here today
to advocate the passing
of the X Prohibition Law,
so that you will not falter
on your path to adulthood.
And if you do, we can
set you straight.
If our X Prohibition
becomes law,
I promise all of you
will be given new PMs!
[gasps]
Wearing these new models will
be mandatory at all times.
For male and female
students alike.
I know change can be difficult,
but the X Prohibition Law has
your best interests at heart.
So if you can recognize
that and voice your support,
the bill can become law
and start saving lives
that much faster.
I can't stress enough your
importance in this process
as independent minds.
In fact, our original plan
was to convince you all
to sign a petition of
approval here today.
But there's been a
change in those plans.
You'll now have the next
few days to debate it
and then sign it on Sunday.
[gasps]
Thank you for your help
in cleaning up Japan.
[TANUKICHI]
Those new PMs, they're just...
[AYAME]
Chastity belts.
Now do you finally get
how dangerous this law is?
And of all the times. This
is a huge monkey wrench.
It's like she knows our exact
plans for the forest.
What, how so?
Weren't you listening?
She wants the students
to sign the petition
on this coming Sunday.
Ten o'clock, right?
Yes, the exact same time
the cordon will be lifted
from Yatsuga Forest.
[gasps]
[WAITER]
What'll it be?
Coffee. Green tea.
And some soda water.
Soda water?
Who drinks that stuff?
I request a tall
orange juice, please!
I know you're angry,
but I think you need
to calm down a little.
Our classmates are nothing
but well-behaved robots.
Now there's no way we'll get
'em to turn their backs
on a morality campaign
and charge into the woods
looking for
panty-soaking erotica.
This move might as well be
checkmate on our struggle.
Our only chance is to get some
erotic pictures out there ASAP
to get the kids'
shorts steamin'.
But, of course, Saotome
can't get in the mood.
You jerk!
It's not just mood, it's
about doing it hands-free!
Could Da Vinci have painted a
naked Mona Lisa with his feet?
[AYAME] Tanukichi, I'm ordering
you to take one for the team.
Oh. This is way nicer
than I've been imagining.
Seems like the perfect spot
to break my creative slump.
Yeah, well just so you know...
What?
I won't be doing any
"docking" with this stalker.
Saotome, we'll sneak you
into Tanukichi's apartment,
past the landlord and
you'll hide in the closet.
Whatever for?
So you can witness
a real live sex scene.
What're you talking about?
[AYAME] I want you to hang
this on your apartment door.
Help her awaken the
dirty artist deep inside!
If you close your eyes,
I bet you'll barely feel it!
Just the tip should be
enough. Just the tip!
Yes, tip would be good!
Knock it off, you two!
[TANUKICHI]
All right,
if all she needs is to see
someone get sexually aroused
this shouldn't be
too hard to pull off.
[sighs]
I can draw from inside the
closet. Just try to forget
that I am here and do
whatever you have to.
Be sure to summon me for meals.
[TANUKICHI grumbles]
Guess I'm not sleeping tonight.
[door creaks]
--[thud]
--[gasps]
[TANUKICHI screams]
[ANNA giggles]
[ANNA] Don't struggle,
my dear. Enjoy it.
[TANUKICHI]
Wait. I know that voice.
[ANNA]
Be patient. I'm getting ready.
[TANUKICHI]
Wait! What? What is this?
It's cold and wet! No!
What are you doing?
[ANNA] I'm so sorry. I don't
know what's come over me.
I've never felt this way before!
The blindfold's because
I'm too embarrassed
to look you in the eye.
I'm afraid I forgot how
to act like a good girl!
[OTOME screams internally]
[ANNA moaning]
[yelps]
This tingling
sensation feels like
the purest thing in the world.
It must be love!
Oh, it's like a pouch of magic
between my thighs
that I must open!
Don't you feel the same magic
filling your underpants,
Mister Okuma?
[yelps]
I have an itch that
I can only scratch
by rubbing back and forth
over your abdomen.
May I please use your
body for this release?
[yelps]
[TANUKICHI]
Wait! Shouldn't we talk first?
I know. I have an idea.
May I spend the night and
share this fever with you?
[gasps]
[seal barks]
[ANNA] What's this
that's risen between us?
Do all boys have this
finger between their legs
pointing skyward?
[gasps]
[ANNA] How can I feel on fire
while at the same time
be swimming in
rivers of pleasure!
[ANNA]
I want to release this
feeling on your body
again and again and again!
[OTOME]
Oh my goodness.
Yes. You have to keep going!
[gasps]
[AYAME]
Tanukichi, where are you?
You forgot to hang the sign on
the door to bait your stalker.
[TANUKICHI]
Crap, it's Kajo!
You fall asleep or something--?
[yelps]
My goodness, this is awkward.
My best friend has walked in
on me feeding my passions
with another student's body.
I thought I was doing the right
thing. The morally clean thing.
So, why do I feel
embarrassed by it?
Perhaps this is why
mother and father
have only given me the
briefest of explanations
about the mechanics
of physical love.
Hold on a minute, Anna.
What're you doing in
Tanukichi's apartment?
[ANNA]
I am so sorry, Ayame.
But I can't seem
to think clearly.
I'm overcome with a mixture of
happiness and embarrassment.
I'm really in no condition
to see anyone right now!
[shrieks]
[TANUKICHI]
What the hell is this?
[screams]
I'm back! I have
the will to thrill!
And if it wasn't for watching
Anna, I'd have never found it!
Must-draw-smut, must-draw-smut,
must-draw-smut! Ah!
I forgot about these!
Curse these infernal PMs!
[gasps]
[OTOME]
If I can't use my hands,
it's mouth time!
It's working! This is what
I've been waiting for!
Seeing the steamy filth
of human passion in person
has changed my life!
[screaming]
Look away, look away, look
away, look away, look away!
[TANUKICHI, AYAME screaming]
[ANNA panting]
[HYOKA] Finally, we can have
a nice chat in private.
[ANNA] What? I don't
think we've ever met.
I'm sorry, that's my fault.
I'm the President
of the Science Club
whose lab was ransacked
today without any notice.
My name is Hyoka Fuwa.
[ANNA]
Hm?
I'd like to know.
Why did you approve a
recent escalated crackdown
on the students of this school?
I assure you, if I've become
more severe in my governance,
It's only to attain a
stronger kind of love.
Oh! Just admitting
it makes me blush!
Huh? What love?
Ah, you're confused.
As long as all our
actions in life
are morally straight and pure,
it becomes that much easier
for us to be loved
and accepted by others.
For example,
say you achieve success in
the classroom, or in sports.
One can then draw
lessons from this
that help acquire manners,
civility, and virtue.
But above all other lessons,
we must master
the self-discipline
to shun the temptations
that are most lewd.
So what you're saying is,
you're attempting to
clean up school morality
because you think it'll
help someone fall for you.
[ANNA]
Yes, that's it!
My adorable pet flies are dead.
and they have only your quest
for moral purity to blame.
Killing pets is neither
virtuous, nor clean.
But you can't look
at it that way!
Any action that suppresses
"toilet culture"
is by definition right.
Besides! As the saying goes,
"Love is justice."
In other words, any action borne
out of love is fair and just.
So, the more just I am,
the more my chances improve
for that beautiful boy
to fall head over heels
in love with me!
[TANUKICHI] Next Episode:
"Dirty Terrorism Benefits Whom?"