[yelps] What the--?
Why's Kosuri in my bed?
[TANUKICHI screaming]
Mr. Okuma, why're you sleeping
with a girl who's not me?
[gasps]
Uh. Oh, well, this
strange girl is my...
[TANUKICHI] If I give the wrong
answer, I'm a dead man.
Uh, well, the reason she's
in my bed is because she's...
...she's my sister, Kosuri,
who's here from out of town
to observe our school.
Yeah. Half-sister.
My dad's a jerk
who sleeps around,
but let's keep
that part private.
Your half-sister?
[TANUKICHI]
Wait! I know!
Kosuri, explain our real,
but complex, backstory.
[KOSURI]
Why so nervous, Big Brother?
Is that pretty girl
the one you're always talking
about having a crush on?
--[ANNA yelps]
--[squelches]
A crush on me?
[KOSURI]
Uhh...
[ANNA]
Yes.
I'm finally the object
of his affection.
I spent the whole night
in a panic watching you two.
It's such a relief to learn
you feel this way about me.
[TANUKICHI]
Wait.
Anna broke in here, saw Kosuri,
and then held a knife over us?
For hours?
[ANNA] And, of course,
it's also a relief
to learn you're his sister,
and not some random tramp.
Now Mister Okuma doesn't
need to go bye-bye.
[TANUKICHI]
"Go bye-bye"?
Traveling makes me nervous.
But I feel so much
safer sleeping next to
the protective bulk of my big
brother's well-muscled body.
[BOTH scream]
Oh, dear! I've been so rude.
Here you are, Mister
Okuma's sister,
and I still haven't properly
introduced myself.
[TANUKICHI whimpers]
Anna?
I did it again, didn't I?
My body's had a mind
of its own, lately.
I'm in love.
So, um, Big Brother,
who is this?
Uh... Oh, right.
Anna's the Student Council
President at Tokioka Academy.
Nice to meet you.
I'm Anna Nishikinomiya.
And over the last month,
your brother and I
have shared a deep,
and growing, affection.
[beeping]
Oh! I lost all track of time!
I'm supposed to go
pick up Miss Tsukimigusa.
All right, Mister Okuma.
See you later, Lover.
[KOSURI]
So you guys are up against
a scary monster like that?
SOX is even braver
than I thought-- Ah!
--[thud]
--[NEIGHBOR screams]
[NEIGHBOR]
Who are you?
And why are you falling
through my ceiling?
[TANUKICHI]
Aw, crap.
[NARRATOR]
The future. Japan.
For decades, "The Law for
Public Order and Morals
in Healthy Child-Raising"
has banned all sexual content.
This law against libidinous
language, in combination
with the Peacemaker
surveillance technology,
has turned what used
to be an island nation
of anything-goes sexual
deviancy into the country
with the healthiest
public morality on Earth.
But, among the douched masses,
are subversives who would dare
oppose this brave new world
free of naughty thoughts.
This is the story of
these sick miscreants!
[AYAME]
Cock and balls!
[door bell rings]
[TANUKICHI]
Hold on.
Oh, hey, Goriki,
what's going on?
Anna says there's
something important
she needs to discuss with
the council in person.
So, we're gonnao meet
in the conference room,
before school starts.
Let me guess,
she ordered you to be
my personal escort.
No, I just wanted
to walk with ya.
[TANUKICHI]
Huh?
You've been so, you know, busy
for the last couple of weeks.
We haven't had a
chance to hang out.
Hm? Someone in there?
Uh. No, it's nothing.
[RAIKI]
Wha?
You hear that?
Just a mouse.
A mouse?
Goriki, why don't
you go on ahead?
I'll catch up later, okay?
[GORIKI]
Hey!
[OTOME]
Jealous and humiliated.
Goriki lashes out and mounts
the only man he's ever loved!
Okuma and his sister
protest the giant,
but there's no stopping
his powerful thrusts!
What are you doing? Stop!
Who is this little person
and where did she come from?
She's a friend of mine from SOX.
She hides and draws lewd pics.
I'm good with my mouth
and my right hand.
Oh, the name's Saotome.
Sox is even more
impressive than I thought.
Kosuri salutes your ability
to draw with your mouth.
All hail SOX.
[AYAME]
This's bad, Tanukichi.
Like the taste of jizz bad.
It's not even nine o'clock
and you're already trying
to make me throw up.
Whoa, hold on, Slick.
Am I to assume that you
know what jizz tastes like?
[laughs]
It's Goriki, right?
You've tasted his man butter!
That's not true!
[OTOME]
Wait, what's so bad?
Like I said, come.
Coming. Having us come in
early means something's afoot.
I think the Decency Squad is
sending a new representative
to help police our school.
[OTOME]
Yes, that does indeed sound bad.
Well, even worse
is the intel I have
saying this person was
trained in lewdness recognition.
And that was at the
same police academy
founded by Anna's dad,
Matsukage Nishikinomiya.
They teach a course in that?
Yep, and not only do
we have to figure out
how to work with this rep.,
we still haven't solved our
Gathered Fabric problem.
This is as bad as having a
dude's load in your mouth,
and then swallowing it
to make him seem special
'cause I don't know...
his feelings?
Again, stop with
the gross examples.
[OBORO]
I am Oboro Tsukimigusa.
And I am here under orders,
from the Decency Squad,
to become your
school's new Prefect.
You're my first
official posting.
But I'm confident you'll find
my services to be helpful.
[ANNA] Well? What do you
think, Mister Okuma?
Not only does Miss Tsukimigusa
have a trained eye
for finding lewd things,
she also knows how to
dispose of them before they
can infect the students.
The mission I've
been given is to remove
all forms of lewdness
from this school,
and I shall not rest until
I accomplish just that.
S'cuse me, Miss Tsukimigusa?
What're you doing to our hoop?
As I've been ordered,
I'm removing anything
I see that's lewd.
And how is a
basketball hoop lewd?
[OBORO] This device is
assembled in such a way
that when viewed
from certain angles,
it resembles a
large prophylactic.
Oh!
There's something inappropriate
about our intramural
tug-o-war rope?
[OBORO]
Yes.
Because rope can also be used
to tie people up, it can induce
perverted fantasies
when held at thigh-level,
as is common in tug-o-war.
Oh.
[GORIKI]
Ugh.
Don't tell me you're taking
our ping pong balls, too.
Yes, with any balls,
there is always a danger of them
being inserted into a butt.
[ANNA]
Oh!
Wait, why volleyball?
[OBORO] The netting resembles
a type of erotic stocking
that can stimulate
lewdness in the wearer
--and observer alike.
--[ANNA] Oh...
[TANUKICHI] This makes
people think of fishnets?
I never knew
volleyball was so hot.
I have to admit,
when you told me she was trained
at the Decency Squad academy,
I got pretty nervous.
But so far, this girl
seems harmless.
Yeah, you're right.
And she's also put gym
class in a new light.
There's so much
erotic fun to be had
with everyday sporting goods!
[TANUKICHI]
You are such a freak.
[STUDENT A] New girl looks
like she means business.
[STUDENT C] There's no way
SOX will be able to distribute
naughty pics with her around.
[STUDENT B]
But she's also kinda cute.
[HYOKA] Miss Tsukimigusa.
Miss Tsukimigusa.
I'm sorry to bother you, but I
have important questions to ask.
Yes. Ask away.
[HYOKA] Please observe the
cover of this amateur comic.
Do you have any thoughts
on why women would find
male-on-male love so enticing?
All I know is that comic is
unhealthy. Give it to me now.
[HYOKA] Wait. Hold on,
Miss. Please don't take it.
Mr. Okuma, tell her it's
okay for me to have this.
That the Student Council
promised to look the other way.
Well, yeah, the Student
Council's okay with it.
But the Prefect's
another matter.
Give it to me.
[HYOKA] No, please don't.
I need it for my research.
What you see as lewd, I see as
an unconventional textbook
of philosophy and psychology.
[gasps]
Fine, you may keep it.
And so that you may
continue your studies
I'll make sure "Please
Don't Hate My Banana"
does not appear on
the banned list.
[HYOKA]
Uh?
Wait, back up a sec,
Miss Tsukimigusa.
Are you sure you don't
want to confiscate that?
It's clearly lewd and unhealthy.
Yes, you're right.
I can't make exceptions.
[HYOKA] No. With all due
respect, you are wrong.
This is not an
unhealthy magazine.
Also a good point.
I'll exclude it.
Where's you backbone?
[HYOKA]
And what about this one?
[OBORO] Well, that's an
easy one. Give it up.
[HYOKA]
Please, no.
This one simply shows how
to make beautiful music
by using the human body
as an instrument.
[OBORO]
Fine, I'll also exclude
"After School Flute Concerto
for Two" from the banned list.
[TANUKICHI] You'd think a
Decency Squad-trained Prefect
wouldn't be such a pushover.
I'm home.
[yelps]
I trust that your day
went well, Big Brother?
Would you like to
have dinner first?
Or would you rather hop
in the tub for your bath?
Of course he wants dinner first.
And after that,
I shall observe
the forbidden "docking"
scene between siblings.
We're not real siblings and
we're definitely not docking.
You are such a downer.
That would've been
a new frontier
of artistic inspiration.
Never mind her, Big Brother.
What's important is that you
tell Kosuri detailed stories
about the many wild
escapades that SOX,
and Blue Snow have been on!
Oh, shoot, that's right.
I did promise Kajo I'd teach
you about dirty joke terrorism.
There is one thing that
I've been wondering.
How did you first
meet Blue Snow,
and what did she do
to get you to join SOX?
Well...
I met her the morning of my
first day at Tokioka Academy.
She saved me from a nasty
run-in with the Decency Squad.
Kind of like how we met,
now that I think about it.
[KOSURI]
Oh.
I wish I could've been there
to see Blue Snow rescuing you.
I mean, what a crazy
sight that must've been.
Equal parts dramatic
and romantic.
Well, to be honest,
at first I was like,
"What is this wacko
girl's deal?"
But, hey, although, Kajo
loves shocking people
with dirty language, deep down
she's very sensitive, and loyal.
She'll never compromise her
beliefs. She's really strong.
I hope I can be
like her someday.
Now that's a makeover.
"Girl next door"
with just a hint
of ravenous sexual appetite.
And with this new look,
you can go out in public again.
What? You just changed her
hair and clothes a little bit.
If you try too hard to
disguise a person on the run,
then they'll stand
out even more.
She'll hide in plain sight.
Well? What do you think?
Oh, uh. It's kinda cute.
I heard about
you two last night.
Guess you got on top of things
and gave her quite
the sex education.
[TANUKICHI]
It wasn't anything like that!
Ha! That was just
a slip-of-the-tongue.
I meant SOX, obviously.
Tanukichi the Virgin is
still way too inexperienced
to teach you anything about sex.
Ha! Yeah, that may be true,
but he was still thorough
in explaining SOX
and its objectives to me.
Also, the stories he told of
Blue Snow became so passionate,
you could feel his affection
for her growing with every word.
He had that look I've heard boys
get when there's a girl they--
That's enough for now.
Well, since she's caught up,
I can brief you both on
SOX's latest scheme.
Thanks to our hard work,
over the last couple months,
Tokioka students have acquired
a working knowledge of porn,
basic docking technique,
and dirty words.
Phase Two will now see
us extend this blueprint
for perversion into
other schools.
Our next target is gonna
be: Zoshigaoka Academy.
This elite morality
school is ranked
in the top 20 for all of Japan.
Getting past security and
onto campus won't be easy,
so we'll start by hiding an
initial batch of dirty materials
directly outside
the front gates.
Well then, I'm volunteering
Tanukichi and myself
for that job.
C'mon, Big Bro, we've got
dirty minds to create.
[TANUKICHI]
Wait, slow down.
So, that's Zoshigaoka Academy.
This spot seems as good as any
for hiding the dirty
books we brought.
[TANUKICHI] Hey, since you're
Kaisuke Onigashira's kid,
you had to have some
experience with dirty things
before you joined us, right?
Yeah, I'm not a
total noob about it.
But compared to the
experience you guys have
with the hard stuff,
I'm pretty much a nun.
My dad only ever let me read
romance books and manga,
but you guys have real pics
of people getting nasty.
You know, it's silly to come
all this way and not go in.
Instead of just hiding porn,
I think I should
sneak onto the campus.
What? No way.
If I can map out
the best hiding spots
and make a timetable of the
security guards' movements,
we'll have free reign to hide
smut all over the school.
I guess that'd be good.
But how will you sneak in?
Kosuri's got a plan
for that too.
She'll simply sign up
for a campus tour
like a prospective student. Bye!
Hey! Wait!
[KOSURI] Don't worry, Bro!
I know what I'm doing!
Do you really think Kosuri
knows what she's doing?
Well, uh...
How can you let her do this?
What if she gets captured
and rats us all out.
When you're with her,
you're thinking too much
with your little head, Perv.
Uh, sorry. To be fair,
she does seem pretty mature
and crafty about these things.
[AYAME sighs]
We'll go off plan this time.
Hell, I'm curious to see
just how helpful she is.
She may advance our
timeline by months.
[ANNA]
Sorry to keep you waiting.
Miss Kajo. Mister Okuma.
What's wrong, Anna?
Why're we meeting back here?
Miss Tsukimigusa has
completed her latest sweep
through the school
collecting all the things
she believes to be lewd,
but I wanted to
get your opinions
before she throws
this stuff out.
I'll warn you. These
are dangerously lewd.
Um, so do-do you guys agree with
her that rolls of toilet paper
are a threat to our
moral cleanliness?
Because she's confiscated
the entire school supply
and now I can't go potty.
Please. Disagree with her.
The fact is, this center can
be lubricated and used by boys
as a receptacle for catching the
liquid release of their stress.
And then the actual tissues
can be used to clean up
spillage on pants,
hands, and or floors.
Yeah, that's not a thing.
[OBORO] Very well, then
I'll remove toilet paper
and toilet paper rolls
from the banned list.
Thanks for changing her mind.
That leaves just one
more thing to look at.
Well, yeah. Those look
like lewd magazines to me.
Oh, that's such
a relief to hear.
I'm so happy the
Prefects I brought in
are getting the
smut under control.
[TANUKICHI]
Prefects?
[AYAME] You mean
there're more than her?
Of course!
[OFFICER A] There he is! One
of the Gathered Fabric goons!
[OFFICER B]
He's headed that way!
[OFFICER A]
Don't let him go!
[gasps]
[yelps]
Um, Anna, are you okay? Anna?
[OFFICERS]
Thank you, miss!
Ma'am, if it weren't
for your help,
another slippery pervert might
have leaked through the cracks.
Yes. You did good work, boys.
Those guys, they've
always admired Anna.
They even gathered signatures
for her Mom's dopey petition.
What do you think, Mister Okuma?
[TANUKICHI]
Of what?
Between Miss Tsukimigusa,
and my new team of Prefects,
the Student Council is turning
the tide... against SOX.
[TANUKICHI]
Uh-huh...
You think... I've done
a good job, right?
My love for you makes me
crave your validation.
But, if you won't
give it to me now,
then I will try even
harder to win your love.
[crying]
This is a map of
Zoshigaoka Academy.
I've added a diagram of the
security guards' daily routes.
[AYAME] You figured this
out in just three days?
[OTOME]
If this information is correct,
it means we can hide our dirty
pictures anywhere on campus
when the guards aren't looking.
Of course, all of my
information is correct.
I got it straight from
official sources
by spying on their
Student Council.
Wow.
I like that you go in
deep to get the goods.
You'd make an awesome detective
in a porno about fisting.
[TANUKICHI groans]
I thrust myself into that
school and probed for days,
and no one ever
told me to pull out.
I even took the opportunity to
go and hide a few magazines.
You are disgusting
and I'm loving it.
Oh, and that's not all I did.
I hacked the school's TV
system so that from now on,
anytime they try broadcasting,
it'll only play that footage
of flies bodymelding.
That's pretty advanced stuff.
You don't have to make
me feel special.
I just did the usual.
No way.
What you pulled off
in that short time,
it shows me that
you do not suck.
I am so hard right now. Wow.
Because she likes you.
When it comes to
our leader Ayame,
I'll do anything anywhere if it
leads to her getting excited!
Like anal thumbing?
Yeah, or even tickling
your flower petals.
[GIRLS]
Yay!
[OTOME] All this talk is
making my paint brush hard!
[sighs]
[KOSURI]
For your next chore, Brother,
you have three minutes
to buy your sister
some chocolate chip
cookie dough ice cream.
Now. Go!
Okay! Coming right-- Hey.
Hold on. Since when
am I your lackey?
You're not my lackey.
You're my brother-slave.
My report made our new
statuses quite clear.
I'm far more useful to the
cause of dirty joke terrorism
than you.
Now get my ice cream, and
when you return, strip naked,
get down on all fours,
and be Kosuri's chair.
How did you get so pervy?
And how did you infiltrate the
Student Council at Zoshigaoka,
anyway?
Looks like the little midget
girl isn't hiding here today.
I find the easiest way
to infiltrate a community
is to create a kind
of "love scandal."
Oh god, what did you do?
[KOSURI]
Allow me to explain.
Zoshigaoka Academy's
Student Council
is comprised of three
boys and two girls.
My first order of
business was to make
the male President and Vice
President fall in love with me
at the same time.
Oh, boy, I do not like
where this story is going.
Oh. Please forgive me.
I thought you'd
understand I only did it
for the greater cause.
What? No.
Plus, I didn't go far
with either of them.
Although, I definitely
have that skill,
if and when the
situation calls for it.
Yep, that's the
advantage of reading
a lot of romance
manga as a girl.
You're crazy!
After the boys,
I befriended the Council's
female Secretary and Treasurer.
Thus ended my first day there.
Was more of a prep
day, than anything.
You talk like this
is a cooking show.
Moving on to my
second day there.
I manipulated the President
and Vice President
into thinking they loved
the Secretary and Treasurer,
and then I upped the stakes.
I said, "you should ask
them to marry you both
in a big ceremony
at the same time".
Don't worry about who gets who,
they're both beautiful girls."
See?
nd the dumb boys went
right along with it.
Because at that point they
were so totally hot for me,
they'd do whatever
I ordered them to.
Then, I turned around
and confessed my love to
the third boy on the council,
who until that moment
I'd completely ignored.
Hold on, slow down.
With that, they were toast.
The girls rejected the President
and Veep's advances,
and all four fell
into depression,
so now they can't even
look at each other.
Meanwhile, the boring third
boy's so excited to win my love,
he does whatever I tell him to.
That's how Kosuri successfully
violated their Student Council.
That's the meanest
story I've ever heard.
You're a little devil!
How can you call yourself
a member of SOX,
while being such a wet noodle?
Well, that can only
mean, from now on,
Ayame will carry on the struggle
with your "sibling" by her side.
But for Ayame this is about
bringing people pleasure,
not hurting them emotionally.
So then, are you gonna
tell her what I've done?
Or are you gonna look out
for your little sister?
I doubt you would rat.
That would mean appearing weak
in front of the girl you love
just to make some silly point
out of misguided principle.
I'm not in love with Ayame.
I see the way your eyes light
up when you talk about her.
It's a dead giveaway.
Ah-ha! See, you don't
deny it, do you?
[TANUKICHI growls]
Oh, no.
Maybe it'd be best if we
took a break for a bit.
Aww. I asked you to get me
ice cream and you haven't yet.
Who shall be punished for
this terrible oversight?
[KOSURI]
There we are.
This is how you'll apologize
to your sweet sibling,
by giving me foot a bath
with your tongue.
Lick, lick, Brother-Slave.
[ANNA gasping]
[ANNA]
Yes. Keep it up.
The more "just actions"
that my army of
Prefects and I undertake,
the more Okuma will love me.
[AYAME] We're in trouble
with this Prefect thing.
And I'm not just
talking about us,
but dirty joke
terrorists everywhere.
Other schools will
see Anna's example
and try to implement
the same strategy.
How's that worse for us?
[AYAME]
To confiscate lewd things,
the authorities must
first recognize them.
That why's veteran teachers
and Decency Squad members
are normally the front line
for policing the young.
But, if ordinary students
are given the ability
to recognize lewdness...
Our own peers could
become enforcers.
In short,
our efforts to teach the normal
students about lewdness
will completely backfire on us.
And serve to create an army
of more effective police.
SOX versus Prefects
makes our struggle
more desperate than ever before.
And in the meantime, we still
have to stop Gathered Fabric
before they damage our cause
again from the other side.
Yeah, but how can
the three of us
stand a chance against
so many threats?
Don't worry. I have an idea.
It's a risk, but we're in deep,
with no other choices.
Are you guys ready?
This war's about
to get hardcore.
[TANUKICHI]
Next episode:
"Do Androids Dream
of Electric Masseurs?"