We haven't found the boys'
urine that Blue Snow stole,
though it seems to
have been a diversion.
A yellow herring, if you will.
Which leads me to believe
the target she really had her
sights on, was this eye exam.
I see, but what was her
nefarious vision for it?
Hm...
Okuma, you have a vast
knowledge of depravity.
Any idea what she
could've been up to?
[ANNA] According to
eyewitness accounts,
students who took the exam were
guided to spell out "va-gi-n--,"
and that's as far as they got.
Sounds fishy. You know what
comes next, Mister Okuma?
[TANUKICHI]
Huh?
Well, I suppose
it might be, uh...
Spit it out, man.
Well, it's possible it's...
Va... gi...
...n...
A...
[BOTH gasp]
That final letter
remains a mystery.
[TANUKICHI] And it's best
you never find out, Anna.
[ANNA]
Hm?
[NARRATOR]
The future. Japan.
For decades, "The Law for
Public Order and Morals
in Healthy Child-Raising"
has banned all sexual content.
This law against libidinous
language, in combination
with the Peacemaker
surveillance technology,
has turned what used
to be an island nation
of anything-goes sexual
deviancy into the country
with the healthiest
public morality on Earth.
But, among the douched masses,
are subversives who would dare
oppose this brave new world
free of naughty thoughts.
This is the story of
these sick miscreants.
[AYAME]
Cock and balls!
[ANNA]
Huh?
What's wrong, Anna?
[WHITE SUIT] We've assembled
the entire school
to honor a talented student
from class three-one
who's earned a special award
in the Spring Art Show.
So now, I invite
Otome Saotome to claim
her suitable-for-framing
certificate.
[TANUKICHI]
Wow, that's beautiful.
And it perfectly captures
what I've always longed for:
A pure and wholesome life.
[WHITE SUIT]
And now, Miss Saotome.
[TANUKICHI]
That's Otome Saotome?
She's so tiny!
Show some respect.
That hurt.
She's small, but her
gifts are enormous.
That girl has won
countless awards.
She's our pride and joy-- Uh?!
[CROWD gasps]
At the moment,
I'm in an unfit frame
of mind, artistically,
to accept an award like this.
[RAIKI] Saotome shredding
that certificate
certainly was a shocker.
But hey, at least
we didn't suffer
any more terrorist attacks.
--President Anna?
--[ANNA gasps]
Yes, indeed. Thank goodness.
That was a huge relief.
Hey, is it just me, or does
Anna look upset to you guys?
[gasps]
Uh, what's going on here?
Well, it's probably for the
best that you don't know.
[bell chimes]
[TANUKICHI]
This must be my fault.
My erotic acts
of terror put Anna
in an uncomfortable position.
[HYOKA]
Mister Okuma.
Do you have a moment?
At yesterday's physical exams,
I heard from someone
who heard from someone
that Blue Snow was
threatening to add protein
to all of the boys'
urine samples.
Uh, okay? What about it?
[HYOKA]
Do you think it's possible
that putting protein in urine
has anything to do
with pregnancy?
--Could protein-enriched urine
--Oh my gosh, protein?
[HYOKA] be the key to cracking
this whole fertility mystery
wide open?
Perhaps protein--
I have no idea!
At last, I've found you,
Tanukichi Okuma.
[TANUKICHI]
Otome Saotome? What are you--?
[OTOME]
Come.
[TANUKICHI yelps]
Wait! All you had to
do was ask me nicely!
[screams]
Please, just listen! I don't
know what you want from me--
[OTOME]
Silence, Dog!
From this day forward,
you shall be my pet.
Huh? Your "pet"? But why
would I agree to be--?
Would you rather I tell
everyone what you did
during the physical exams
or how good you look in pink?
[TANUKICHI gasps] I-I don't
know what you're talking about.
[OTOME]
Don't bother denying it.
I was on the roof and saw
everything with my own two eyes.
[gasps]
[OTOME chuckles]
All right, fine. What
do you want from me?
[OTOME]
Oh, nothing major.
[OTOME] I just need you
to lend a hand and prod me
out of my temporary slump.
I don't understand.
How can I "prod" you?
[BOTH gasp]
Pervert alert!
Wait, Kajo! It's not what it--
[OTOME] Hmph! Stupid wench.
Irritating as usual.
[TANUKICHI]
"As usual?"
Does that mean there's some
kinda bad blood between you two?
Well, actually, that's
not entirely unrelated
to the thing I'm asking
you to help me with.
See, I want you to aid me
in my romantic pursuit
and that awful witch
is my romantic rival.
Huh?
Oh, What?
Is the idea of me being in love
really that preposterous to you?
Stuff a sock in it,
you impertinent pet!
Come on now, Saotome.
What in the world do
you think you're doing
in a place like this
with a boy like that?
[OTOME] Unhand me, you
gargantuan gorilla! I mean it..!
First at the assembly this
morning and now this.
You've been a bad
little girl all day.
I'm sorry, but even scholarship
students have to obey the rules.
Okuma! We'll finish this!
You think it's over? Ah!
Well, it is most certainly not!
We shall meet again!
[TANUKICHI]
Otome Saotome caught me.
Oh, so that explains why
she boxed you in like that.
How'd you get that? Huh?
You really are a
foul-mouthed pervert.
No, I'm not!
[WAITER]
Sorry for the wait.
Compliments of the
lovely lady right here.
[AYAME]
Heh.
Thanks.
Well, don't worry
about the girl,
'cause she's only interested
in getting what she wants.
I don't think she'll tattle.
It seems like you
know her pretty well.
[AYAME] I've had my eye
on her for a while.
I'd hoped to get her to
draw some dirty pictures.
[TANUKICHI] Seriously,
is that all you think about?
This is good for us.
It's an opportunity to drop
some sexual knowledge on her,
then we can seduce her
into joining SOX.
[TANUKICHI]
Huh?
[AYAME]
Come on, wouldn't it be a blast
to fill such an innocent girl's
mind with facts about sex
until her sweet little
hymen hula hoops?
Not really, no.
Are you sure about that?
'Cause if it goes well,
then I can help you
get in good with Anna.
Ugh. So predictable.
I shouldn't be surprised,
though. It's the same old story.
You nasty boys are
always pitching tents
in your pants like
you're on safari
with rhinos, elk, and unicorns
running through your heads!
Hey, I am not "horny" for Anna!
[AYAME] It's nothing
to be embarrassed about.
I mean, so what if
all you really wanna do
is stick your custard-cannon
in her glazed donut.
What's wrong with that?
Okay, now look, Miss Kajo,
let me be perfectly clear here.
I do not have any
desire to do the thing
you just described with Anna.
[gasps] Wait, don't tell me,
it's her fudge hole
that you're after?
You know that's
not what I meant!
Anna is a pure-hearted
young woman.
And for that, I look up to her!
I'll be satisfied
as long as I can be
an effective council member.
All this chastity
is grossing me out.
How can it be gross?!
[AYAME] Let me tell you
something, Tanukichi.
You can't just remove
the nuts and bolts
from boy-girl relationships.
In the end, she wants every
inch of your pure hard-on
and you should be
looking up her skirt.
[TANUKICHI] How dare you soil
my flowery words in mud!
The act of lovemaking
isn't something that's dirty
or immoral.
When two people gradually reveal
their intimate parts
to one another,
bringing together their
most sensitive areas
in sweet harmony,
it's their continued acceptance
of each other that forms a bond.
And it's not just a physical
thing. It joins their hearts.
Don't you see? That's why
dirty jokes are beautiful.
[AYAME]
But let's end the levity here.
[groans]
Anna doesn't find
any of this funny.
I'm sure you've already
noticed that about her.
[TANUKICHI]
So, tell me,
do you have any idea what's
been bothering Anna lately?
[gasps]
[TANUKICHI]
Anna has a stalker?!
[AYAME]
Yup. For the last week,
she's been receiving
letters and creepy photos.
[TANUKICHI]
Is she safe?
Please, if you think there's
anything I can do to help,
just name it.
I'll do whatever it
takes to protect Anna.
No, there's nothing
you can do for her.
But what if--?
[AYAME]
Oh, don't worry. She'll be fine.
Right now, you need to
focus on Otome Saotome.
If you do that,
then I can concentrate
on keeping Anna safe.
[TANUKICHI] You know,
when you talk like that,
it almost seems like you
really are her best friend,
like you actually
care about her.
[AYAME]
What do you mean, "like"?
[TANUKICHI] I thought the whole
best friend thing was an act.
[AYAME sighs]
Ten years ago, she befriended
me right at the moment
when I was most depressed
about not being allowed
to tell dirty jokes.
It's because of Anna
that I'm able
to blend in with polite society
now, even if it is just barely.
I really... blow her big time!
You mean owe her!
[AYAME] Anyway, I'll leave
the matter of Otome Saotome
in your capable hands.
[AYAME chuckles]
[TANUKICHI] If this is the
socially acceptable version
of you that Anna
helped foster,
I'd hate to see what
you used to be like.
[OTOME] An artist needs plenty
of calories in order to create.
Gotta eat!
So, how exactly do you think
I'll be able to help you
in your quest for love?
[OTOME] I haven't come up
with any specifics yet.
That's why I asked you
to meet me here.
[TANUKICHI] Well, who is
it you have a crush on?
[OTOME gasps]
I-I can't tell you that.
I will say,
I worry sometimes that I might
be making my love uncomfortable
or that maybe they
even detest me
and those fears are what
keep me up at night.
Hey, why are you grinning
at me like that, you creeper?
Is the notion of someone
like me being in love
really that ridiculous?
Uh, no, no, not at all.
In fact, I think
it's kind of sweet.
And really, there's nothing
for you to be embarrassed about.
I've got my heart
set on someone, too.
Oh?
Hey, I've got an idea!
How about we both
utter the names
of our secret
sweethearts in unison.
If you do, then I'll forgive
your insensitive grin.
Oh, all right, fine.
[gulps]
Okay, you ready?
One... two....
--[beeping]
--[TANUKICHI] Uh?
Anna Nishikinomiya!
[yelps]
You fiend, you've deceived me!
I'm sorry, I'm sorry!
I was distracted!
I got an email in my PM.
[growls]
[OTOME] Don't test me! If you
try to back out of our deal,
I shall inform the Decency
Squad of all of your crimes.
[TANUKICHI]
Okay, uh, my crush is--
[TANUKICHI] Wait, if Saotome's
infatuated with Anna,
then there's no way
I can tell her
that I'm in love with
the exact same girl.
What do I do here?
Should I just blurt
out some random name?
But whose?
What's taking you so long?
I'm about to hit "send."
Three... Two... One...!
It's Ayame Kajo!
Oh, so you got seduced by that
horrible little harpy, did you?
Perfect!
Together we'll drive a wedge
between Ayame and Anna.
And then I'll swoop in and
fill the harpy-shaped vacancy
left at Anna's side!
And we'll live
happily ever after!
[TANUKICHI]
Hold on, just a minute!
Yeah, what?
Did you forget?
I'm a villain who's
been deceiving Anna.
I mean, you can't possibly
wanna team up with someone
in such a complicated
position, right?
Huh? That's the dumbest
thing I've ever heard.
[TANUKICHI]
Huh?
[OTOME]
Anna never seems happier
than when she's chasing
after perv-terrorists.
In fact, to me, it
almost looked like
the two of you were just
playing a really fun game
of hide-and-seek.
[OTOME]
Well, anyway,
I see no reason why we
shouldn't join forces.
Does that answer all
of your questions?
We've gathered here today
in order to discuss next month's
signature-collecting campaign
for the X Prohibition-- Uh!
Are you okay?
Oh, you just dropped
your water bottle.
[ANNA]
I'm sorry, I--
I can't take it anymore!
We all know this low-down,
dirty dingo did it!
Mister Goriki, you're
wrong about him.
Mister Okuma's not
that kind of boy.
Madame President,
you still don't see it?
Okuma! This is your
handiwork, isn't it?
No, I had--
[RAIKI]
Liar!
Stop this!
I'm telling you.
Mister Okuma would never
do anything like that.
Uh, sorry, I guess.
[ANNA] I apologize for not being
more forthright about this,
but there's no need
for you to worry.
The matter will be
resolved soon enough.
Are you sure, Anna?
[AYAME] In case you hadn't
noticed, Goriki likes Anna.
Though I'm not sure
he even knows it.
[AYAME] That's why he
totally flipped out
when Anna suggested
you join the council,
and why he's had it
in for you ever since.
Now with this stalker situation,
his instincts to protect
Anna have kicked in
and only hardened him.
[TANUKICHI]
Poor Goriki.
Ha! By the way,
in case it wasn't clear,
I meant it hardened his heart,
not his dick, though maybe.
Gee, thanks for clarifying that!
Can't you go five whole
minutes without being gross?
Five holes? That's
a lotta orifices.
[TANUKICHI]
I give up.
The sad thing is: Goriki is
still better off than most.
Ever since the Law for Public
Order was put into place,
all of the ways people used to
express love have been censored.
So eventually,
it got to the point
where they forgot how to love.
Even worse, there are more
and more people who feel love
but don't realize it.
I wonder if that's what
Saotome is dealing with.
[AYAME]
Huh? What do you mean?
Oh. Nevermind. It's
nothing, just-- Uh...
Fuck me!
Shit! Piss! Fuck! Cunt!
Cocksucker! Motherfucker!
Tits! Shit! Piss! Fuck! Cunt!
[TANUKICHI]
Why're you freaking out?!
[AYAME]
It was staring us in the face!
Once you put all
the pieces together,
then there's really
no doubt that Saotome
has got to be Anna's stalker!
She doesn't know how
to show her affection
for Anna in a healthy way,
so she's resorted to sending
creepy letters and photos!
Wait, you don't really believe?
It all makes total sense.
That's why she glared at me
with all the envy of a
horny little virgin boy
eyeing a lacy double-D
brassiere for the first time.
Oh! But if I don't handle this
delicately, I'll ruin my chance
to have her draw dirty, dirty
pornographic pictures for me!
[yells]
[TANUKICHI] Kajo, just calm
down a bit, all right?
[AYAME] Huh? Go down
on your dick all night?
[TANUKICHI] I didn't say that!
Come on, be serious!
Listen to me, I'm telling you
there's no way Saotome
could be Anna's stalker.
[AYAME]
Do you have any proof?
Just my instinct.
Oh, your instinct?
Instinct is crucial.
It's also known
as your "libido."
[TANUKICHI]
That is not what "libido" means!
[AYAME]
Oh, who cares what it means?
The important thing is,
you should trust your instincts
and always act on them.
Which is beautiful.
All right then, I have faith
in your assessment
of Saotome's character.
Wait, are you serious?
Oh, I just had the
greatest idea ever.
We'll trap the stalker and
get Saotome to capitulate.
We can screw both things--
I mean, do both things at once!
Are you cuckoo-banana pants?
You want to lure the stalker?
That's right.
See, I'm gonna
dress up like a boy
and then go out on a date
with Anna in the park.
When the stalker sees this,
he'll lose his mind,
go mad with pure primal
jealousy, and rush to attack me.
[RAIKI]
It's too dangerous!
I can take care of myself.
[RAIKI] Then at the very least,
let me be your date.
[AYAME] But you have
no dating experience.
Besides, if you
pose as her date,
the stalker will be too
scared to show himself.
No, you should stay hidden
so you can jump out
when we need your muscle.
[RAIKI groans]
Just in case, Mister Okuma,
you keep watch here.
Oh, okay.
Very interesting.
Well, the two of us will have
to follow them to the park then.
That way, as soon as the
stalker exposes himself,
I shall rescue Anna.
And when I capture
that scoundrel,
I'll capture Anna's
heart, as well,
and then it will
throb only for me.
Uh, throbbing hearts
are nice and all,
but what exactly
does that have to do
with why you're shaving my legs?
Isn't it obvious?
We've gotta disguise you
so that the stalker
won't suspect anything.
Why am I a girl again?
Hey, pull yourself
together, woman!
We cannot let those
two out of our sight.
[growling]
Darn you, Ayame!
How dare you be so
close to my beloved!
[TANUKICHI]
I hope Anna will be okay.
[OTOME breathing heavily]
[screaming]
Who told you you could peek?
What? You have nothing
to be embarrassed about.
I can't believe you call that
a slump. It's beautiful.
[crying]
[TANUKICHI]
Hey! What's wrong?
[OTOME] This is the one way
I have to express my love!
The only pictures I want
to draw are of Anna!
[TANUKICHI]
Huh?
It may sound strange,
but up until recently,
I had never used anybody
as a model for my artwork.
Before, I created
all of my paintings
from images that were floating
around within my mind.
But Anna is the first person
I ever really wanted to paint.
Since the day I met her,
I've spent every waking moment
trying to commit
her image to canvas.
But even after
hundreds of attempts,
I still couldn't get it right.
And I could never figure
out what was missing.
I thought if we became
lovers, maybe it'd be clear.
But I don't have the ability
to emote outside of my art.
And that's the reason
why I'm in a slump.
My only purpose in life is to
create art, and yet tragically,
all I can do now is desecrate
Anna's image like this!
She must be utterly
disgusted with me!
Saotome.
[rustling]
Saotome? What in the
blazes are you doing here?
Stop loafing about
and start winning our
school some more art shows!
Huh?
Goriki? Where did you come from?
Is that who I-- Wait, Okuma?
[grunts]
What're you up to out here?
[TANUKICHI]
Wait, it's not what you think!
[yelling]
Get away from her!
Anna!
[TANUKICHI]
I won't make it!
Eat fist, Twerp!
[STALKER A]
Mama.
Is that man gonna be okay?
Oh, don't you worry.
I got him in his vitals.
I guess, that's Kajo for ya.
[OTOME]
This isn't over yet!
Don't just stand
there, Tanukichi!
Anna, why are you with him?
How could you just throw
away our love like that?
Hey, look out!
[OTOME yelling]
[TANUKICHI]
Goriki, catch!
What do I look like--?
[TANUKICHI]
Huh?
Which one was I trying
to save just now?
You tart!
What? Tanuki-- Okuma?
I'm sorry! Please forgive me!
[AYAME]
Mister Okuma!
Hurry, call an ambulance! Now!
I'm on it!
[OTOME]
Wait, what about me?
Isn't there any way
I can save the day?
[ANNA]
What's happened to me?
What is this odd sensation?
[ANNA squeals]
Why do I feel so
warm... down there?
[TANUKICHI] Next episode: "The
Saying Goes, Love Is Justice."