[AYAME]
Wait, what?
Yes. Yes. I see.
Understood.
'Kay, I'll talk to you
later, Mighty Cock.
Can't you ever just
say goodbye?
What's wrong? Did
something bad happen?
[AYAME]
That was the coffee shop.
Apparently we just
got an invitation...
...from Sophia Nishikinomiya.
Whoa, hold on.
Do you think that means
she knows that we're SOX?
I'm not exactly sure.
But still...
...we have no choice.
We have to go.
Just like a hard dick whose
tip is already inside a pussy,
we can't stop now.
[TANUKICHI]
However, at the time,
we still didn't realize it.
None of us could have known
that SOX's biggest crisis...
...was still to come.
Ooh.
So Sophia Nishikinomiya
really invited all of us
to come meet her in Nukumi?
Nukumi was once a hot
springs district.
From what I gather,
it was a pretty happening
place back in its day,
but now it's been
completely purified.
I hear there are no traces
of its former glory.
[KOSURI]
Hey, what's that?
Oh. Dad gave me this.
Way back when.
[ZENJURO]
Here.
What is it?
When you get older and
you wanna go to Nukumi,
you be sure to bring that
with you, all right, son?
Trust me, you won't regret it.
[AYAME]
Your father is still behind bars
for being an erotic
terrorist, isn't he?
So I wonder--
What do you think this is
supposed to be used for?
[KOSURI] Oh, maybe it's
some kind of adult toy.
Maybe you put Okuma's
banana in that...
[BOTH] ...gaping hole
right there in the center!
Not a chance!
This place has been declared
the nation's purest city.
It's hard to believe
now that it used to be
a debaucherous hot
springs district.
Though, the "pure
city" classification
is really just a title.
It's more of a health resort.
[OTOME] So, is that
Health Land over there?
The place she invited us to.
Yeah, they advertise
"Health Baths" and
"Health Restaurants".
And it says here that
they're a self-contained,
full-service health
resort that even offers
"Health Sports" and
"Health Rec Rooms."
Huh? "Health Sports"?
"Health Rec Rooms"?
What the health is
that supposed to mean?
[TANUKICHI]
Health Sports include dodgeball,
triangular base, folk dancing.
Of course, the folk
dancing isn't co-ed.
Meanwhile, the Health Rec Room
features card games, Parcheesi.
And a karaoke
machine fully loaded
with Decency Squad-approved,
morally uplifting songs.
Guests will wake up at
a healthy six a.m. and,
before breakfast, perform a
series of healthy exercises.
Curfew is at a healthy nine p.m.
[AYAME] Brown rice, organic
vegetables. MSG-free ramen.
Ew, gross. It's all so healthy,
I think I'm gonna be sick.
[AYAME] Sheesh, I mean
it's not like I was expecting
Sophia to come out
and welcome us herself.
But come on, it's weird that
nobody's here to greet us,
don't you think?
I don't see any
other guests around,
or anybody who works
here for that matter.
Are we the only
people in this place?
[RAIKI]
Is-Is that?
Okuma!
Never thought I'd bump into
you here. It must be fate.
Hey, Goriki!
Oh. You must be
Okuma's little sister.
I've heard so much about you.
Oh my goodness,
so you're Goriki.
I hear you and my brother
have become very close.
What? People are saying that?
How embarrassing. Right, Okuma?
Might be a little bit
awkward when the two of us
are alone at a meeting now.
So, what in the heck are
you doing here anyway?
Well, you see,
Anna's mother Sophia
personally invited me to come.
Here, take a look.
This is the same
invitation we received.
What's going on here? Ah!
President Anna?
Oh, um.
I thought I smelled Mister
Okuma's manly scent
wafting through the air, but I
didn't realize he wasn't alone.
Anna, are you the one who
sent us all these invites?
[ANNA]
N-No. In fact, I'm just here
because I received an
invitation from my mother.
But it's weird. I've
looked all around this place
and I can't seem to
find her anywhere.
So what do you think
we're doing here?
Maybe this is a trap.
[ANNA gasps]
[ANNA]
Could it be?!
Is, uh... something wrong Anna?
My mother must've
reserved this entire resort
just for me and Mister Okuma.
[OTOME gasps]
[OTOME]
That gives me some ideas!
Yeah, I'm pretty sure that's
not what's happening!
Say, whatcha drawing
over there, Saotome?
Hey, Goriki, maybe you and
Okuma should both whip out
your pencils and then
freehand each other.
No, we shouldn't!
[laughing]
No, Okuma and I would
just make a mess!
Huh, I've been trying
to get ahold of my mother
via the PM system
for a while now,
but there's been no response.
Well, there's no need to panic.
Let's just give her a little
more time to contact us.
Good thinking, Mister Goriki.
This is Health Land, after all.
We should all go take
advantage of the Health Bath.
[OTOME] Hey, where's Anna?
This was her idea.
She'd better not be
on the boys' side.
Oh, don't worry.
Tanukichi's not alone,
he's with Goriki.
Two unpeeled bananas soaking
side-by-side in a steamy bath?
Inspiration for
my next comic book
is bubbling out of me
like a hot spring!
[KOSURI]
Forget that bunch of bananas,
I'm more impressed
by these melons.
Not too big and not too small.
A perfectly proportioned
pair of flotation devices.
Hey! Stop that!
Kosuri, stop! Get off me!
Ooh! A new fetish!
You knock it off, too, Saotome!
[TANUKICHI] He sure is
taking his sweet time.
[door opens]
Hey, Goriki, what's the deal?
It took you long enough.
Looks like no one else is here.
We've got the whole
place all to ourselves.
[gasps]
Anna, what are you doing here?
Mister Okuma.
So, uh, where did Goriki go?
[ANNA giggles]
Oh, he's wandering
around the resort
in search of
nonexistent manju buns
that some adorable girl may
have asked him to find for her.
[TANUKICHI]
Not cool!
[ANNA] Oh, Okuma. At last
we're alone together.
Today...
[panting]
...is the day I finally
give you my Love Nectar!
[TANUKICHI yelping]
Aw, don't try to resist me.
If you're too loud,
Ayame and the other girls
next door will hear you
and come over and we wouldn't
want that, now would we?
Please.
Anna, just let go of me, okay--?
[moaning]
[muffled screaming]
[ANNA]
Ah!
Feels so good!
[muffled screaming]
[ANNA]
Ah!
And now, my sweet man,
I shall devour your
delicious Love Nectar
straight from the
throbbing source!
[SOPHIA]
No, I have a husband!
[SOPHIA screaming]
--[AYAME] What was that?
--[OTOME] What happened?
Ew. Is she dead?
[AYAME]
Sophia Nishikinomiya!
Did I hear somebody
scream in here?
[AYAME, OTOME gasp]
Beautiful!
Ew, that's gross.
[ANNA gasps]
Mother!
[TANUKICHI] This says
it was sent by... Anna.
I've never seen that
invitation before.
So what then?
Somebody wanted to trick Sophia
into coming out here, too,
just like all of us?
[MALE VOICE]
Exactly.
[ALL]
Hm?
[MALE VOICE] It was I who
personally invited each of you
to come here to Health Land.
Is that White Peak?
Wait, no, Black Peak?
He's covered in black panties.
What did you do
to my poor mother?
Nothing. Don't you worry.
She's just sleeping.
I drugged her.
Oh, Mother!
Ah.
Black really is... best.
Black is so beautiful
and it reigns supreme.
And no, I don't
have any connection
to that piece of garbage
known as White Peak.
Oh. Allow me to
introduce myself.
You may call me Base Black.
Anna, are--? Uh!
[chuckles]
Ah, at last, all the players
have been assembled.
[BASE BLACK giggles]
[AYAME]
Hold it right there!
Miss Tsukimigusa, come in.
Where are you right now?
[OBORO]
As instructed,
I'm patrolling outside
of Health Land.
And I've got a
Prefect-in-training with me,
just in case something were
to happen to you, Miss Anna.
Well, something's happened!
Get over here as
quickly as you can!
Copy that, miss.
We've got some trouble. Come,
it's time for us to move out.
Oh! All right!
[BOTH scream]
It's no use. He's already gone.
Well, we should at
least get dressed.
[OTOME screaming]
[AYAME]
What's wrong?
My clothes have been stolen.
And my underwear.
[ALL]
They're black?
How awful. I'm way too young
to be wearing black panties.
Oh no! Mine are black, too.
I wonder if mine are.
My poor mother.
She's fine. She's just sleeping.
Uh. I feel kinda funny with
us all dressed like this.
So, I'm gonna go get all
of our bags from the lobby.
Wait for me, I'm
coming with you.
Seriously, how are you
embarrassed by this?
Aren't you the same
girl who runs around
in nothing but a bed sheet
yelling obscenities?
Well, yeah, but that
is completely different.
[TANUKICHI gasps]
Where'd all of our stuff go?
Ah, yes, I knew you would
bring it along with you.
You are Zenjuro's son.
Hold on. Do you know my father?
Yes.
And I also know that thanks
to you, I now hold the key
to opening the trove where
the treasure sleeps.
Wait, the trove where
You mean, that's what you've
been after this whole time?
Yeah, I've heard of
that phrase before.
A long time ago at Nukumi,
it was rumored that there
was a mansion in which
all of the treasures of
the country lie sleeping.
"Treasures"? You mean...
like old porno mags and stuff?
Oh, no. Nothing nearly
as trivial as that.
We're talking way
more spectacular.
Yes, that's right. And now
I have the key to it all.
[laughing]
[KOSURI]
Hey, there he is!
[BASE BLACK]
Hm?
Give us back our clothes!
Where're our bags?
He must have them.
What is that? The weird thing
that's sticking out of your bag?
[AYAME] It's a key to
unlock lewd treasure.
How lewd?
I cannot just stand here, and
allow you to access such filth.
[OBORO]
Miss Anna!
Miss Tsukimigusa?
Why are you dressed like that?
[OBORO]
I apologize for our appearance.
We fell into a pit and
got completely soaked.
And then, for some reason,
this lingerie was down there.
There's nowhere for you to
run now. Just give it up.
[chuckles] No, how about
we have a duel instead.
Do you honestly think
that you stand a chance
against all of us?
Well, since this place used
to be a hot springs district,
I humbly propose that
we use a dueling method
that was popular in the
hot springs of yesteryear.
Hold on, you're not
talking about. Oh no.
Baseball?
So what are the rules? Tell us!
We play strip rock, paper,
scissors and after each match,
the loser removes an
article of clothing.
Then, whichever side is stark
naked first, loses the duel.
Hey, but wait a second,
you're wearing like
a thousand pairs of
black panties right now.
How's that fair when we're
all wearing next to nothing?
There's no way we can win.
[BASE BLACK]
What's wrong?
You refuse to honor the
traditions of this sacred place?
Fine, we accept.
If you're dueling method
is truly righteous,
then we shall take
it on wholeheartedly!
Um, Anna, what are you doing?
Now. Who has the guts
to face me first?
[STUDENT A]
Me!
[ALL]
Huh?
As a Prefect-in-training,
I should be the
first to volunteer!
All right, game on!
[BOTH]
Rock. Paper. Scissors!
Woohoo!
[chuckles] Well, I can afford
to allow your side one victory.
He's going right
for the chest first.
Well, that's better than the
crotch, though, isn't it?
[whimpering]
[chuckling]
[whining]
No! I don't think I can go
through with this after all!
Tell the Disciplinary
Committee I quit!
Perhaps this sort of duel
was just a little too intense
for a delicate young lady.
Oh well, on to the next one.
I'm not afraid.
Hey, when Goriki strips,
that'll be our chance.
Our chance for what?
Just trust me. And whatever
you do, don't look at Goriki.
[BASE BLACK]
Let's go!
[BASE BLACK, RAIKI]
Rock, paper, scissors!
[growls]
All right. Everybody look away!
[gasps]
[BASE BLACK retches]
Now!
Hey, wait!
Okuma, Ayame, listen!
The rest of us will
handle this degenerate.
You two focus on taking
that obscenity-unlocking key
and hide it somewhere
no one will ever find it!
Whatever you say, Anna. Thanks.
We can't let you prevail.
By doing what's righteous,
I will finally get the
dreamy Mister Okuma
to love me like I love him!
All right, come on, Tanukichi,
let's go and find that
lascivious pleasure trove.
Okay, so do you
know where to look?
According to legend,
you have to take a cable car
all the way up a mountain.
A cable car?
[TANUKICHI]
I don't see one on the map.
If it's a cable car
that you seek,
I did find a rusted-over
something not too far from here.
Whoa, Fuwa?
What're you doing here?
[HYOKA] I came to collect
some unusual insects
that are indigenous
to this area.
Would you like to see them?
Just take us to the cable car.
[AYAME] It doesn't
exactly look operational.
Is there anything
we can do, Fuwa?
Well, I'll take a look at
the switchboard and see.
I couldn't help but notice
your state of dress.
Has your cucumber gone from
its battle-ready stance
to spore releasing yet?
Don't read into it, 'kay?
[gasps]
Look, Tanukichi, it's moving!
Hey, Fuwa! Keep holding it!
[AYAME]
Tanukichi, hurry!
Hurry! Get up here, now!
Grab my hand!
[yelping]
Tanukichi!
[TANUKICHI whimpering]
Well, for this good deed,
I'll reward myself
by indulging in some
salacious Goriki and
Okuma comic books.
[footsteps]
[TANUKICHI sighs]
I thought I was a goner.
[BOTH gasp]
[TANUKICHI] This hunk
of junk is a deathtrap!
Actually, it's not.
That wasn't the
cable car's fault.
It was hers!
Mister Okuma! Wait for me!
[TANUKICHI yelps]
Hey. Watch it!
I won! I beat that creep
at his weird duel!
Please tell me that I'm
worthy of your love now!
Hey, do something
about her, would ya?
Like, I don't know,
jump off to lure her away.
What?! Jump off?!
Are you insane?!
[ANNA]
Mister Okuma!
[AYAME]
What the...?!
Mister Okuma! Please
give me what I desire!
[TANUKICHI]
Can't... breathe... dying.
[yelping]
[ANNA]
Mister Okuma!
Oh no, Anna!
Don't worry. Even
from this height,
Anna's superhuman strength
will protect her.
I guess this is it?
Let's go in.
Okay.
[TANUKICHI]
What a waste.
The Decency Squad.
I don't know why they had to
completely destroy everything.
We should get outta here.
[TANUKICHI]
Huh?
Look, even if that thing
in your bag is the key,
there's nothing left
here but ruins.
Kosuri?
Wait, no, that's not her.
Look closer.
It's a giant wooden dildo.
[TANUKICHI gasps]
What is it?
[BOTH laughing]
It's my father. I can
tell that he was here.
Your father's a
great man, Tanukichi.
Yeah, he really does go
all the way, doesn't he?
[TANUKICHI chuckles]
Kajo, look, the mannequin
there is still intact.
It's almost too clean.
Like someone took
care of it or something.
Uh?! What the...?
Wait, look. See that?
[TANUKICHI gasps]
[TANUKICHI]
Huh. I wonder.
A perfect fit!
Turn it then. Give it a try.
Huh? You sure? Do you
think that it's safe?
What'll happen if I do?
There's only one
way to find out.
Go on, we've come this far.
We owe it to our predecessors.
Let's finish what they started.
What if the Decency
Squad broke this thing?
[AYAME]
I doubt it.
Huh? Why is that?
[AYAME] Just look. Everything
around it's rusted over,
but the axle is
totally pristine.
It's never been used. Not even
by those Decency Squad jerks.
This thing won't budge at all!
Don't you dare give up!
Whoa, Saotome?
[AYAME]
Were'd you come from?
[OTOME] I snuck off while the
others were retrieving our bags.
The wooden dildo?
No, it's Kosuri!
Sorry to show up late.
But I'm here to
help you out now!
Now all of SOX is here,
working together!
Then let's turn it up
to the Power of Four!
[ALL grunting]
[NARRATOR]
And now,
a breeze charged with many
thoughts blows through,
exposing the pure white of
innocence, which burns the eyes.
[ALL gasp]
Look! It's opening up!
[AYAME]
Tanukichi, keep turning it!
Girls, help me push!
You got it!
[NARRATOR]
Dearest perverts,
you've endured such hardships
to get to this sacred place.
Now, like an erect cock,
stand proud and firm.
And without hesitation,
thrust passionately
down your chosen path.
It's a tribute to mankind's
undying lust for the erotic.
Yeah. I feel the history
of sexuality here.
[gasps]
[TANUKICHI]
Base Black!
You've grown up well, Tanukichi.
After we played rock,
paper, scissors,
he showed me a secret passageway
that led me to this place.
But why would he help you?
[KOSURI] He says that he
used to fight right alongside
Zenjuro Okuma.
So when he saw you on the news
rescuing all those hostages,
it reminded him of his glory
days with your father.
So that's why he wanted
to show us this place?
He was only pretending to be
the bad guy, unlike White Peak.
That's why he dressed
up in black panties.
Uh, no. That part was real.
This dude actually has a pretty
serious black panty fetish.
He's kind of a huge freak.
[BOTH]
Uh...
[OTOME]
It takes one to know one.
[BASE BLACK chuckles]
[TANUKICHI]
So,
what're we supposed to
do with the treasure?
The world isn't quite ready
to behold its beauty yet.
We have to preserve this,
for future generations to find.
[OTOME]
In that case,
what do you say we leave
our signature behind, too?
Some sign we were here?
Took you long enough.
I was worried about you.
Sorry 'bout that.
Oh, I see that you
made it back already.
So go on, tell us
what was up there?
Something graphic and
disgusting, no doubt.
Well, no.
Actually, there was nothing
disgusting up there.
In fact, it was
quite... lovely.
Oh, wow, really?
Well, that's a big relief.
--[explosion]
--[gasps]
[ANNA]
Miss Tsukimigusa!
That cable car was used
by co-ed passengers
and I fear it may have
even been designed
for indecent co-ed
fraternization.
It was lewd and
had to be destroyed.
Well, if it wasn't before,
that secret stash will
be protected now.
I wonder when that treasure
will see the light of day.
Hopefully, it won't
have to wait long.
Maybe we can't know
when, but still...
...I do know that
this boring world
where the concept of
dirty jokes doesn't exist
has gotta end someday.
And until then...
we'll keep fighting.
[chuckles]
[chcukles]
[NARRATOR]
For decades,
"The Law for Public
Order and Morals
in Healthy Child-Raising"
has banned all sexual content.
This has turned
Japan into the country
with the healthiest
public morality on Earth.
But there are subversives
who would dare oppose
this brave new world
free of naughty thoughts.
This is the story of
these sick miscreants,
and their passionate heroism.
Cock and balls!