[TANUKICHI]
Watch out!
[AYAME]
Huh?
[yelps]
[gasps]
[groaning]
[AYAME]
What was that?
[COP A]
Blue Snow's out of the bus!
[COP B]
Get her!
[TANUKICHI]
Kosuri, no. Don't do this to us.
[KOSURI]
Cram it, "Big Brother."
I'm done with you
limp-noodle clowns.
There'll be consequences if
you don't get out of my sight.
Now. Get off.
[TANUKICHI]
Stupid traitor!
[COP C]
That's Blue Snow's accomplice!
[COP D]
Get him!
[COP E]
Freeze, creep!
[WHITE PEAK] Thanks for
the assist. I owe you.
[KOSURI]
Oh, don't worry about it!
I'm just happy to be a
part of Gathered Fabric.
[KOSURI] The Decency Squad's got
their hands full chasing SOX,
and we've still
got all our guns.
This is our chance
to change the world.
Let the Revolution begin.
[chuckles]
[WHITE PEAK] Yes. Let's
take this bus for a spin.
Next stop: Zoshigaoka Academy!
Well, it'll work out somehow.
Guess I'm in the clear for now.
But still, how am I gonna
get home dressed like this?
[HYOKA]
Good evening, Mister Okuma.
What the hell are you doing,
Fuwa? Why're you in the bushes?
The Decency Squad
stationed me out here
to spy on any hijacked
buses that drove past.
Oh, right.
Ayame said you were
helping determine
which of Gathered
Fabric's guns are fake.
That's the current
state of affairs.
But I'd hoped things would go
better than they have been
and I'd be home now.
The situation's grown more dire.
Than it already is?
I take it then your wanderings
have kept you from
seeing the news.
[ANCHOR A] The terror of this
morning's Gathered Fabric-led
bus hijackings continues
deep into the night.
The terrorist group has
re-routed the 39 captured buses
to the prestigious
Zoshigaoka Academy.
Decency Squad sources tell
us that Gathered Fabric...
Fuwa, I can't stay here.
I gotta find Ayame now!
[SQUAD BOSS C] Has Gathered
Fabric issued any new demands?
[UNDERLING A]
Yes.
They're demanding food and
drink for their hostages
as well as a massive
shipment of new panties.
[SQUAD BOSS C]
New Panties? That's odd.
Isn't the group's M.O. normally
about stealing used panties?
[UNDERLING A]
Wait, sir.
They've just sent an image.
My god.
What's wrong?
"If you don't meet our
demands for the new panties,
we'll take pictures of our
hostages wearing panties
on their heads and send them
through the PM network."
How vile! Most of those students
have promising futures!
[SQUAD BOSS A]
Uh!
If they want bushels
of new panties...
Oh, god, I hope I'm wrong.
[TERRORIST A] Just take them
off and put them in the basket,
then take one of the brand new
pairs provided and put them on.
[TERRORIST A] We'll be
back in about three hours
to collect those.
So make sure you stink
'em up real good, ladies!
[STUDENT C]
This is so humiliating.
[STUDENT B] Yeah, they're
not even bikini cut.
[breathing heavily]
Hurry and put them on! Oh!
Please stop doing that.
Can you just put on
your own fresh panties,
and leave me alone?
[OTOME]
Oh, god. Yes!
They're so cold!
[OTOME]
Why does this excite me so much?
Huh?
No, my sweet pencil!
[TANUKICHI]
Sorry, Kajo.
I'm moving through
town as fast as I can,
but it's hard dressed like this.
[AYAME] Oh, I get it.
I'm in the same boat.
[TANUKICHI]
Hear about Kosuri?
[AYAME] Yes, I know.
But did you see the news?
Yeah.
I'm worried this may
be checkmate for SOX.
[AYAME] The hostage
thing will resolve itself
sooner rather than later.
The real question is
what happens after that.
The media will still
report that this incident
was supported by SOX.
We're guilty by association.
Oh, and it gets worse.
With Kosuri in custody,
the career of her father,
Keisuke Onigashira,
will be ruined.
And when that happens,
all the erotic terror
groups he backs will fall.
The whole country's gonna
think we're violent criminals.
They'll use it as
an excuse for why
we need the X Prohibition Law.
[TANUKICHI] But come on, there
has to be something we can do.
[AYAME]
In a perfect world,
we would storm the
Academy ourselves
and take down Gathered Fabric
before the Decency Squad does.
Great! Then let's meet
up and attack them!
I would, but SOX doesn't
have the manpower.
There're 39 of them.
And now they're probably armed
with Kosuri's air
guns and stun guns.
Thanks to Gathered Fabric, the
Decency Squad finally has us
right where they
always wanted us.
Desperate and powerless.
This reminds me of something
my dad once said.
"No matter how hard you try,
it's impossible to defeat a fool
who's certain of his
own righteousness."
[HYOKA] I disagree with
that so-called wisdom.
[TANUKICHI]
Fuwa!
[HYOKA] I have proof what
your father said is wrong.
Because fools end
up getting drunk
on their own righteousness.
Then fall into a
form of insanity.
I know someone like this.
Wait, do you mean?
Yes. I mean Anna Nishikinomiya.
She has been
brainwashed to the point
that she would do anything
as long as she believed
it to be righteous.
If you told her it was
the right thing to do,
she would even commit murder.
And she'd do it with
a smile on her face.
A person who thinks like that
will never see victory
in the long run.
Anna's failure is inevitable.
[TANUKICHI]
She's so far gone.
Or is she?
Hold on a sec.
[HYOKA]
Uh?
[AYAME]
What is it, Tanukichi.
[TANUKICHI]
I have an idea.
One that can bring hope
to our hopeless situation.
Sure, there's a good chance
it'll be a miserable failure,
and it's incredibly humiliating
the more I think about it,
but still.
I... will defile myself.
[HYOKA]
Don't worry about it.
We've already seen
you defiled repeatedly.
In yaoi manga with Raiki.
In the latest one, he gives
your rear input a real workout.
Kajo, I have a proposal.
[KOSURI]
This is so cool.
You've done more in one day
than SOX has in a whole year.
Mister Peak?
I have some ideas for what
the next scheme should be.
[WHITE PEAK]
Next scheme?
We'll use the hostages as
leverage to escape Japan,
go overseas and win allies,
and then return and liberate
the country from the prudes.
[WHITE PEAK]
Are you actually so foolish
you believe we can
accomplish all of that?
--[KOSURI] Uh... Uh?
--[intercom squeaks]
[TERRORIST A]
Commander White Peak.
We present you with the day's
second White Offering!
Good, I've been waiting. Savior!
Descend!
Oh, yes! What an
intoxicating aroma that is.
[KOSURI] So, um, Mister White
Peak, sir, as I was saying.
Yes, what? What's so important
that you interrupt my rolling?
[KOSURI] Well, if we stay here,
it's only a matter of time
before the Decency
Squad catches us.
True. And that's why I'm
going to enjoy every last
musky undergarment that
this paradise has to offer.
What about the
revolution you promised?
[WHITE PEAK]
That was mere sophistry.
Escape from the country?
A guerrilla war?
Don't you see that those
efforts would be pointless?
Nothing would change.
You should be embarrassed
by your foolishness.
You're a loser,
White Peak! A fraud!
And I'm gonna feed you something
other than your
precious panties!
[KOSURI yells]
I win, creep! Huh?
How... did you?
[WHITE PEAK]
Silly little girl.
When an electrical weapon
hits a wet target,
the shock only travels around
the outside of the object.
And, since my body is wrapped in
these beautiful white panties,
soaked with wine, I'm simply
too moist to be shocked.
I... I can't...
Losing... strength.
[SQUAD BOSS C]
Status report!
[SQUAD UNDERLING A] Things seem
to have calmed down, for now.
We just carried in the third
delivery of meals and underwear.
Our analysis shows that their
weapons are non-lethal.
They simply don't have the
strength to defend the Academy.
Then we shall attack at once.
[MATSUKAGE]
No. It's too soon.
[SQUAD BOSS C]
Matsukage? Sophia!
Why do you suggest we hold off?
[MATSUKAGE] Crushing them
now would be too easy.
And the hostages aren't
in any immediate danger.
But no one else knows that.
Let White Peak play
devil for the public.
"Play Devil"?
The longer this
panty farce goes on,
the more freakish they seem.
And the more the public
will support our cause.
Passage of the X
Prohibition Law.
That's right,
just like what happened with
Zenjuro Okuma ten years ago.
[TANUKICHI] According to
the blueprints Kosuri made,
there's a secret entrance
to the Zoshigaoka campus
via the mountains
directly behind it.
Yeah, that's perfect.
We use that entrance
and slip past the media,
the Decency Squad,
and Gathered Fabric,
and right into the
school's juicy bits!
Kajo, now's not
the time for that!
The hard part is finding where
they've locked up the hostages.
And finding Takuma Ichinose
and our former friend, Kosuri.
[beeping]
[OTOME]
Hello? Can you hear me?
[TANUKICHI] Saotome!
Thank goodness, you're safe!
Yep!
I tricked White Peak's goons
by drawing some good
old-fashioned healthy pictures.
[TERRORIST B]
Hmph.
[OTOME] They're keeping most of
the hostages on the third floor.
And I'm pretty sure
I overheard them say
that all panty deliveries
are to go to White Peak
in the school
principal's office.
Comrades, let me know
when you're set to attack,
and I'll drop my pencil and
help you from the inside.
Well, all right then.
There's our intel,
just need manpower.
Tanukichi.
This plan you came up with,
are you really gonna do it?
[TANUKICHI]
Uh.
I know it's not our normal M.O.,
and it creeps me out a bit,
but it's the best way
to get the help we need.
[laughing]
[AYAME]
Oh, Tanukichi.
You've come so far under me.
Emphasis on "come."
Yep.
[AYAME] Since you're now fine
with despoiling your body,
there is one other
thing I wanna confirm.
And what's that?
Do you like... naughty language?
Fuck yeah, I do!
It sounds weird coming from your
upper mouth, but I'll take it!
I'm a boy, I don't
have a lower mouth!
[BOTH chuckle]
The SOX counter attack
begins at once!
Yeah!
[ANCHOR B] We have an update
from Zoshigaoka Academy.
Decency Squad officials
tell us Gathered Fabric...
A dangerous pervert's holding
half our student body hostage
and Kajo and Okuma
are still M.I.A.
They're making the entire
Student Council look bad! Hm?
Come to think of it,
I haven't seen President
Anna much either.
She's taking another
long shower.
[RAIKI] Another? How clean
does she have to get?
Ohh.
When you're depressed
about life,
nothing beats thinking of
Mister Okuma in the shower
and letting your
Love Nectar flow.
Ohh. No matter how
many showers I take,
there's still nectar to be
squeezed from my loins.
Uh.
Who did--? Ah!
[ANNA]
Ow, ow.
Is someone there?
[gasps]
That smell... Is that the
manly scent of Mister Okuma?
[sniffing]
[gasps]
The only thing I
smell now is soap.
I guess I just imagined my love.
[OTOME growling]
[STUDENT A] I'm not looking! I'm
not looking! I'm not looking!
[AYAME] Put down your
pencil! It's go time!
Let the liberation begin!
[KOSURI]
I should've known better.
Ayame was right
all along. I'm so sorry.
I don't know what it is you
regret, my purple-headed friend,
but they're never
going to hear you.
[TERRORIST A]
Commander White Peak, sir.
The next offering is
ready for your enjoyment.
Oh, how I've waited.
Yes. Savior, decend unto us!
[TERRORIST A]
Hey! No!
What? What's going on?
[thud]
[AYAME] Long time
no smell, dick cheese!
SOX is back to crush your ego.
And if you really piss us off,
we'll crush your balls, too!
[WHITE PEAK] What? SOX?
But there are only two of you.
It's you who will
be crushed! Go!
[TERRORISTS]
Yeah!
[AYAME]
Stun guns.
That ought to teach them.
I don't want weapons
in our schools
any more than I
want dirty pictures.
[AYAME] Huh. Nice
assist, President Anna.
Hold on, President?
SOX is allied with
their Student Council?
[AYAME] We've got more
friends than just them.
Who the hell are they?
[TERRORIST G]
Put me down!
[ANNA]
Please don't misunderstand
the partnership on display.
I'm helping out SOX
because you're the more
disgusting threat.
Also, I desperately want
to get my hands on the bag
of underwear you stole
from my lover, Mister Okuma,
during this morning's
bus jackings.
[ANNA laughing]
[TANUKICHI]
Yup.
This is my risky,
dirty plan in action.
Take advantage of
Anna's lust for me
in order to get help and
manpower from the establishment.
[ANNA] That smell... Is that
the manly scent of Mister Okuma?
[TANUKICHI] She's like a dog in
heat! I gotta erase my smell!
[TANUKICHI] Ha, ha! No,
Miss, I'm a member of SOX.
I'm actually here to see if
you'd like to join forces-- Ah!
I'll never join
forces with you guys!
[TANUKICHI]
Wait, please! Just hear me out!
If you ally with SOX,
you can destroy far more
terrible terrorists.
And you'll get Mister Okuma's
underwear all to yourself!
[gasps] Mister Okuma's undies?
[AYAME]
Hey, why are you spacing out?
If you're playing pocket pool,
do it on your own time!
[TANUKICHI]
Right!
[TERRORIST D]
What the hell--?
[gasps]
[ANNA]
I... smell... Mister Okuma!
[AYAME groans]
Gathered Fabric! Attack!
All of our fallen enemies shall
have their underwear removed!
Don't panic! Single
file lines, people!
Stop right there!
I wanna see all hostages get
back into that classroom!
Or 'else, we'll flood
the Net with pics of you
wearing panties on your heads!
[OTOME]
Not so fast!
Eat some of these!
[TERRORIST K]
What?
[TERRORISTS]
Panty rain!
Yes!
Wait a second,
this is just a drawing.
It's fake, but I
think I smell a--
A strong musky scent
lingering in the crotch area!
[HOSTAGES yelling]
[OTOME chuckles]
This is proof that 2D is still
better than 3D any day.
Emergency!
SOX and Tokioka's Student
Council and Prefects
are freeing the hostages!
[SQUAD BOSS C]
What now?
Please tell me this is a joke!
Why would Anna
work with criminals?!
[MATSUKAGE]
Calm down, dear.
She's probably just
getting intel on them.
Oboro is with her.
You really think
that clueless dummy
can protect our little girl?
[OBORO] The state considers
the placing of undergarments
over one's face to be a lewd
act. I must remove them.
Anna.
[TERRORIST D]
Uncle! Uncle! Uncle!
[AYAME]
It's over, White Peak.
[WHITE PEAK]
Hmph.
All right. I shall
surrender as a gentleman.
Well, how very sensible of you.
Now, I'll alert the police
to your surrender, and--
[TANUKICHI]
Wait, Anna! Watch out!
[gasps]
[WHITE PEAK] You naïve
little girl. Alert this!
The day is mine!
[ANNA screaming]
[AYAME]
Anna!
I'm free!
Miss Anna, hold on!
This is for tying
me up, you freak!
[screaming]
[WHITE PEAK]
This can't be. No! It's swollen!
[AYAME]
Now, attack again!
[ANNA]
Uh, right!
Oh, why must you
punish me for my fetish?
It's society that's gone mad,
not the man sniffing panties!
Poke.
[yelps]
[AYAME]
President Anna!
Darn that stun gun.
[AYAME]
His tool is his weakness,
but the fleshy part's
such a hard target.
He flaps it around
so much I'm dizzy!
[TANUKICHI]
Area B!
His nipples!
They're the only spot
he's left wide open!
Great thinking, Tanu--
Err, Taint Boy!
[ANNA]
Taint?
[AYAME]
Take this, you pervert!
Bullseye!
And now it's my
turn to punish you!
[WHITE PEAK groaning]
[AYAME] Let's finish him,
President Anna!
[ANNA]
Right!
[AYAME]
We're sending you home,
where the only panties
you'll be smelling...
...are your momma's!
[WHITE PEAK screaming]
[REPORTER A]
Breaking news!
Someone's just been thrown
through a window. Is that--
[REPORTER A screams]
[AYAME]
The nightmare is over.
Yeah.
I'm afraid I can't stick
around to celebrate.
We'll settle our score later.
[ANNA]
Miss Tsukimigusa, follow me!
We have to find
Mister Okuma's undies.
I was promised Mister
Okuma's underwear!
Looks like somebody is
sorry for what they did.
[KOSURI] I'm sorrier than
I ever thought possible.
I won't betray you again.
[AYAME]
Good!
Now, time for my
big victory speech
on the importance
of teen sexuality.
[ONLOOKER A]
Hey, what's that?
[AYAME] SOX has defeated the
panty-stealing terror group,
Gathered Fabric!
What is she talking about?
Since when do terrorists
fight each other?
[ONLOOKERS murmuring]
[AYAME]
I wish to become a dirty joke!
What does that mean?
She's insane.
Yeah, I don't get it.
[TANUKICHI] Well, folks,
that's the girl I like.
[AYAME] I'm serious. I want
to become a dirty joke.
Why? Because our society
scorns their very existence,
and calls them "evil"
and "unnatural."
But dirty jokes have a right
to exist and be heard.
And I have a right
to aspire to be one.
It's true, that by the standards
of contemporary society,
everything we erotic
terrorists do may seem wrong.
And if we act rashly,
because we're so
certain we're right,
we'll become no different
than those we fight against:
The misguided utopians
who want a boring world
where the concept of
dirty jokes doesn't exist.
The ramblings of a madwoman!
We still have time to
cut the broadcast signal
before this goes
nationwide, right?
[UNDERLING A]
I'm trying, ma'am,
but one of the stations
is refusing our orders.
Which one? Arrest all of them.
[UNDERLING A]
Well, ma'am,
it's the station
owned by Onigashira.
[AYAME] What's the point
of making jokes at all
if they have to be clean?
Jokes appeal to us because
they can be so wrong.
Jokes get us excited
because we don't know
how people will react to them.
It's because they're
devilish they can seduce us.
Because they're twisted
they can make us laugh.
I became the devil
because I believe
that laughing at what's sick
can make society healthy.
To destroy this boring world
where dirty jokes do not exist!
Now, go fuck yourselves!
Heh. I didn't think our society
could still produce
someone with real guts.
Darling, what're you saying?
[UNDERLING A gasps]
What is that thing?!
[AYAME]
Ta-ta! Bye-bye! Dick-dick!
Didn't think we'd tie up all
the loose ends that quickly,
but here we are!
What's wrong?
Nothing. Just surprised is all.
That speech was the most
serious you've ever been.
[AYAME]
How rude!
Everything I've told
you since the day we met
has been deadly serious!
But I admit, I can also be
stubborn and single-minded.
And I'm glad that you're not.
I'm mean it.
Thank you for being
you, Tanukichi.
[TANUKICHI]
Why are you saying this?
[AYAME]
You're a fully realized person,
and when your soul's
laid bare, buck naked...
...you can be twisted and fun.
It's like you're a dirty joke.
I am?
And I love you
as much as balls.
[TANUKICHI]
Um... Kajo?
[AYAME]
What?
Who is this guy you love?
I don't see him like you do.
You can't decide that based
only on what someone else says.
At the end of the day,
who you are's up to you.
The choice must
come from within.
You know, if your
head was a pussy,
and my finger was a Johnson,
I just gave you three orgasms
with only three pokes.
We're perverts in love!
Perverts in love!
Kajo, there's no
one better than you
at making a tender moment
really disgusting.
Got that right. Well, let's go!
[AYAME laughing]
So, everything's over. Why're
you still hanging out with us?
Oh, I told you I was sorry!
Please don't look at me like I'm
an extra, superfluous nipple.
Love you. Love.
All right, that's enough.
You're weirding me out.
Do you have to
suck up so much?
[KOSURI]
Of course.
To make up for turning traitor,
I will be Ayame's slave.
I'm gonna be on her like
glue until one of us dies!
[beeping]
Hello? What's up?
Is something wrong?
What'd you say?
[TANUKICHI] Next episode:
"Dirty Jokes Forever."