(thunder booming)
(airplane buzzing)
(thunder cracking)
- [Phantom Narrating] My
name is Phantom F. Harlock.
It was when I was flying in a thunderstorm
from Port Moresby across New Guinea
heading for Rabaul in New Britain.
As an ariel explorer my
life long cherished dream
was to conquer the air
throughout the whole world.
The only thing that stood in my way
were the Owen Stanley Mountains.
With its highest peak soaring up
to 5,030 meters above sea level
the mountain people feared
calling it the Witch of
the Owen Stanley range.
My name is Phantom F.
Harlock and this plane
I call Arcadia is like
my own flesh and blood.
My companion to share my
fate and my youth in Arcadia.
Sharing those precious youthful days.
Flying high in the sky.
If it ever ceases to fly my
life will come to and end.
With a full load of fuel the
plane was heavy that day.
I couldn't gain any altitude
and Arcadian's engine gasped desperately.
The sound from the gasping cylinders
was almost like my aged
irregular heartbeat.
I and my Arcadia flew through
ravines wherever possible.
(airplane buzzing)
(dramatic music)
But the Owen Stanley
Mountains just stood there
high and rigid and cold, totally
dominating Arcadia and me.
(tense music)
Arcadia and me, we had
to face bitter defeat
for the first time in our
entire life in the sky.
While turning back swallowing my pride
something made me look back.
(echoing laughing)
The mountain, the mountain was laughing.
With my Arcadia I had
been continuously blind
believing we could never be defeated.
I jettisoned all the fuel only
leaving enough for 10 minutes of flight.
Lightening the plane I'd staked
everything on those last 10 minutes.
(dramatic music)
My name is Phantom F. Harlock.
The plane and I shared
every moment of my life.
My youth and Arcadia, the life I lived
flying in the sky with conviction.
There is no regret so
long as men do not abandon
their dreams their
dreams will never vanish.
(echoing laughing)
(dramatic music)
(thunder cracking)
(echoing laughing)
(dramatic music)
(thunder cracking)
(echoing laughing)
(orchestral music)
(glass shattering)
(screaming)
(gasping)
- [Man] The third clock,
impact gun damaged.
- [Man] Starboard rear
engine room damaged.
- [Man] The ship's thrust 80%.
- [Man] An enemy's ship approaching.
Take phase three combat position.
(dramatic music)
- [Phantom] The dream is over now.
Earth is the only place
where Earthmen can live.
We must submit to defeat,
but have we done our best?
Hmm.
- [Man] This is Illumidus
Earth Occupation Force calling.
Follow our instructions and
land your ship at base 446.
If you resist we will take immediate
measures to destroy your ship.
Six minutes, 55 seconds before touchdown.
Maintain present course
and strike your colors.
Do not attempt to resist.
- [Maya On Radio] Broadcasting
on frequency band 6050.
With variable micro-frequency.
The sun disappeared yesterday,
but the sun will rise again today.
Continue to have faith
in the ever rising sun.
- That, that voice is--
- Believe in our future.
Everyone living on Earth.
Although the ground has been burnt--
- [Phantom] Maya.
- [Maya On Radio] Turning
everything into ashes.
All will revive again.
The sky is ever so blue.
The sound of the ocean unchanged.
This is our own planet, Earth,
so long as we keep our dreams.
- Oh, listen, that's the
underground radio from Earth.
- [Maya On Radio] It will never disappear.
- That's right, it's the
voice of Radio Free Arcadia
broadcasting from somewhere
on occupied Earth.
- [Maya On Radio] Keep a song
in your heart for tomorrow.
Let us stop crying and
stand firmly on the ground
for we shall all have a wonderful future.
(dramatic music)
(clanging)
(screaming)
(whirring)
- Stupid landing.
- That stumblebum.
No wonder we lost the battle.
- [Man] The Solar Federation.
(mocking laughing)
Some invincible armada.
- Move, move.
(gasping)
- Move.
(footsteps rapidly thudding)
(suspenseful music)
- Captain, isn't your name Harlock?
Remember you're surrendering.
I'll take your sidearm.
A very amateurish landing,
but I guess it was inevitable
due to the poor condition of the runway.
Still, I think your secret
purpose was to disable your ship.
- That's right.
- [Zoll] You are to present
yourself to headquarters
and that will conclude all of your duties.
- Haven't we met before?
- During the battle at the
Castlemagne Star Cluster
you disabled my ship by
blowing a hole in the hull.
- I see.
Now that you've won you must feel great.
- It was a very long battle
and many times I felt
my last hour had come.
You were a formidable
adversary, especially your ship.
- Thank you.
And what is your name?
- Zoll, of Tokarga.
- Torkarga.
Planet Torkarga?
That lost the war against
Illumidus a long time ago?
- That's right.
(suspenseful music)
Report at 10 o'clock.
Wait.
Didn't you hear me?
I told you to report to headquarters.
- [Phantom] I still have
two hours before 10 o'clock
and there's a place I wish to go.
- Your families' place?
- I have no family.
- Remember to report at 10 o'clock.
- I will be there.
What's wrong, don't you trust my word?
- Just be careful walking in the streets.
If you get killed and fail to
return I'll be responsible.
- [Maya On Radio] This is
the voice of Free Arcadia.
The sun set but it will rise again.
There's no future for those who
don't believe in the future.
The ones who believe have endured.
Some day we will meet again
and some day join forces
to start living our future together.
Don't let the fire die down.
Keep even the faintest spark
with a firm belief in our future.
(footsteps rapidly thudding)
(guns firing)
(screaming)
- [Man] Over here.
(dramatic music)
(thumping)
(groaning)
(gun firing)
(thumping)
(yelling)
(gun firing)
(clanging)
(dramatic music)
- I see no reason not to use a man
who won the highest hero medal in combat.
- Sir.
- Apparently Zoll you thought
too highly of the Earth man.
(dramatic music)
- I am here.
What do you want of me?
- This is the Illumidus Occupation Forces'
supreme commander General Zeda.
- And I am Harlock.
The captain of the Death Shadow.
And there's nothing more to say.
- Don't get smart Earth man.
(bones cracking)
(groaning)
- Let go of him Harlock.
Reading books is not going
to help you win any battles.
Books will never help you win against us.
- We've gathered a
staggering amount of data
on you Earthmen since our occupation
and according to our computer analysis
Earthmen are easily acclimated
to a new environment.
In other words even though
they've been hostile
up until today now they're
wagging their tails at us.
- But the fact is Earthmen
are definitely not cowards.
- [La Mime] Let me present
Prime Minister Triter
of the Illumidus Occupation cabinet.
- Ah, good evening.
- Prime Minister Triter
I see you have failed to
capture The Rose once again.
- Ah well, I assure you that I will
arrest and execute her the next time.
- My orders are to identify the voice
of Free Arcadia at any
cost, not to execute anyone.
And once we find out there are ways
of taking advantage of it.
- Oh, this man is--
- The ex-captain of the evacuation ship.
- Ah, Harlock, this man is dangerous.
(gasping)
Well, if you'll excuse
me, I have things to do.
- A useless individual.
- By the way Harlock General Zeda
has seen your combat record
and is willing to give you work,
that is if you want the job.
- I decline.
- So you are also stubborn, you may leave.
- Take your food coupons and get lost.
Go anywhere, there is
nothing for you to do.
You will never have another
chance to fly again, understand?
La Mime, give him some coupons.
- [La Mime] Just a moment please.
Your food coupons.
Keep your temper and eat while you can.
The provisions on Earth are running short.
Eat now or you'll starve to death.
(jazz music)
(chattering)
- Hey, this guy has a black collar.
Why don't we show him some fun?
- Leave him alone, he might be the one
who scratched one of our ships in battle.
- Scratched our ship?
I bet you're right.
(laughing)
- Hmm?
(dramatic music)
- [Phantom Thinking] I know how you feel.
All we can do now is eat and wait.
We've been defeated but we still exist.
- Just don't die.
(laughing)
- [Phantom] And I was
feeling sorry for him.
(groaning)
- Why you dirty yellow rat.
Take that and go back to
the gutter where you belong.
And now you're stealing my food.
(groaning)
- That'll fix him.
(laughing)
(groaning)
- Well?
(laughing)
(thumping)
(chuckling)
(grunting)
(thumping)
- Go get him!
(angry shouting)
(thudding)
(bonking)
(groaning)
(laughing)
(thumping)
- Now that things have gone
this far, drop dead all of you!
(laughing)
(thumping)
Whoa.
(laughing)
- [Woman] Huh?
What are you doing?
(sirens blaring)
(laughing)
- That was fun.
My name is Tochiro and I'm leaving now.
- So am I.
(sirens blaring)
(cat scowling)
(glass shattering)
- What a waste.
- But why, why do you go
around acting like a beggar?
- [Tochiro] You could call
it a single handed revolt.
- Revolt?
- [Tochiro] That's right.
- [Phantom] How can you call it
a revolt without any weapons?
- [Tochiro] If you had a
weapon would you revolt?
- Weapon?
But they're impossible to get.
(laughing)
- [Tochiro] But there's
always a way to get anything.
Here.
- Why that's-- Sort of old though.
But how did you?
- Better than nothing.
(vehicle screeching)
- Someone is coming.
(gun firing)
- [Zoll] Brought you here
because the memory areas
of both of your genes were
put through analysis simultaneously
and we analyzed 3,000 years of your past.
- Why'd you do that?
- Is this a torture? (yelling)
- [Zoll] Listen to me.
You both have the same common gene factor.
See where those two lines
overlap now and then,
the place where it sparkles.
- [Phantom] What does that mean?
- [Zoll] It indicates your memories.
Both of you have inherited
some identical memory genes
going back to your distant ancestors.
- Identical?
- With me?
- Some time ago I happened to obtain
some strange data on both of your genes.
Both of you show the same
memory based on a common experience.
Now I am going to revive
that memory for you to see.
(machine whirring)
(dramatic music)
(gun firing)
- Follow me.
We'll land on the autobahn for refueling.
(airplanes buzzing)
(screaming)
(clanging)
Well I guess that does it this time.
- [Tochiro] Why are you waiting there?
Get out of there before it blows up.
- This, I've got to...
- Ah, a C-12-D.
- [Phantom] This gun
sight has never failed me.
In the Battle of Britain or in Africa.
What are you doing?
(flames whooshing)
(explosion booming)
(dramatic music)
- It's too bad your plane
was destroyed like that.
- Ah, I never thought that would happen.
- Your landing gear wasn't strong enough.
It's not your fault.
- Are you Japanese?
- Yes.
I came on a technical exchange
as an optical instrument designer.
My name is Tochiro Oyama.
- I'm Phantom F. Harlock Junior.
- Harlock, then you're the
one who wrote this book huh?
- My father wrote it.
- I see, My Youth in Arcadia.
Only real men could understand this book.
- Maybe.
- [Tochiro] But why are you
flying an Iron Cross plane?
- I'm just doing it to pay the rent.
By the way Tochiro are you a samurai?
- [Tochiro] My father's a farmer.
The first manned rocket in the world.
(explosion booming)
- I guess it ran out of fuel.
- A lot of things are
running out fuel these days.
- But my battle's not finished yet.
- [Man] We've put all the
remaining fuel in that new one.
It's the only plane left.
(dramatic music)
(gasping)
- Why did you do that?
No wonder this country isn't
going to last much longer.
- [Phantom] Are you interested
in things like that?
- That's right.
My work is to develop
a new precision sight.
I was handling it very carefully,
but your rough landing on the
road caused it to be smashed.
- I'm sorry.
- This is a stupid war.
- I guess we're both feeling frustrated.
- If they'd only let me work
without all this fighting
I could work on a great project
with a future in it
like going to the moon.
- There'll come a time some day
when man will be able to go there.
(airplanes buzzing)
(guns firing)
Tochiro what's wrong?
Hurry and go.
- But there's no place where I can go.
- Go to Wiesbaden and then to Switzerland.
- The Allies already
took Wiesbaden last week
and they're between here and
the Swiss border right now.
But I sure wish I could continue
my research in Switzerland.
(bomb whistling)
(explosion booming)
- [Phantom] There's not
much room, but get in there.
It's not bulletproof so if
you get hit don't blame me.
- [Tochiro] Don't worry, I'll be alright.
(suspenseful music)
(gasping)
- Hang on, here they come.
(guns firing)
Tochiro, you alright?
- [Tochiro] I've got a good view.
Here comes a Spitfire on the right.
- And here we go.
And now.
(gun firing)
Strange, no rudder.
Tochiro are there any
broken wires back there?
- Everything is fine.
- Is it?
A strange reaction.
Got to get lower.
So, I'm the only one left.
(dramatic music)
Switzerland.
10 more minutes.
Tochiro, you want to go back to Japan?
- [Tochiro] Of course I do.
Harlock, don't you want to go home?
- I do.
And I want to return to Arcadia,
the home of forests and lakes
and a beautiful paradise like
the one in ancient Greece
where my memories of youth go racing
through the rich green fields.
The home of the pirate
knight Harlock family.
As the end of the journey approaches
all my clansmen yearn to
return to our lovely home.
We all hear the voice of the spirit
of the pirate knight of Arcadia.
(engine rumbling)
(wind howling)
Tochiro, next stop Switzerland.
500 meters.
Tochiro Switzerland is just on
the other side of that river.
Hurry up.
Come on out.
What's wrong?
(suspenseful music)
(groaning)
Tochiro, your hands.
You held the broken wire
together with your bare hands.
That's why the pedals felt so strange.
I'm sorry Tochiro, I didn't know.
- But I'm not dead.
It's just my hands, they're a little numb.
- Wait for a second.
- [Man] Hey over here.
I found them, over by the wrecked plane.
(gun firing)
- Somebody's coming.
- They're French resistance
who penetrated into German territory.
Don't worry I'll help you across.
(dramatic music)
Tochiro take this with you.
- Why that's--
- It's the one from the plane.
Take it with you.
- But this is your--
- I would only give this to
someone whom I could really trust.
Someone who was truly a friend.
Someone I could believe in.
- Harlock.
- [Phantom] Here.
(gun firing)
Farewell.
- Harlock what are you going to do now?
- I'm not the type who
would run off like a coward.
A pirate must always be ready
to answer for what he has done.
Tochiro never give up your dream
and make the most of your life.
(gun firing)
(gasping)
- Harlock.
- I'm glad I could meet you
at the end of this stupid war.
I wish we'd met in different times.
- [Man] He's down in the river.
Circle around to the right.
- Harlock.
Stay alive!
Harlock, I'll remember you
for the rest of my life.
My whole family will never forget you.
Our friendship will never never die.
Never die.
(birds squawking)
- [Tochiro] Over a thousand years ago
our ancestors had been friends.
- But I wonder why Zoll
gave the book back to me.
- Harlock congratulations.
My suspecting you of
being in the underground
has all been cleared up.
- [Zeda] And I am quite pleased.
- According to Zoll's report
the results of the analysis
proved you totally innocent
along with your friend here.
- I must ask your friend to leave us alone
for I wish to talk to Harlock.
- Harlock.
We must have you pledge your
loyalty to Earth once again.
- I have always fought for this planet
in accordance with the laws
and rules of Earth at the time.
- Alright, good enough.
We have decided to send a volunteer army
to the planet Tokarga.
- Tokarga?
- And I am assigning you the task
of transporting the troops.
- Why are you sending an army there?
Why must Earthmen have to
go to Tokarga to fight?
- Let me remind you that you have
pledged your loyalty
to Earth and so have I.
And now we are being
forced into a position
where we must either
allow the mother to die
or kill the stray dog.
- So now Earth is the mother
and Tokarga is the stray dog.
- For Illumidus the entire planet
of Tokarga is of no further use.
- You intend to annihilate
Torkarga, to liquidate it?
And who in the universe can decide
whether a planet is useless or not?
Every single living thing in the universe
has a right to life and now the mission
to destroy Torkarga has to be carried out
by Earthmen using my hands?
The whole idea stinks.
- Come back.
We must cooperate with the Illumidus
by sending a volunteer army.
It's the only way they'll guarantee
the safety of the Earth.
You think the whole idea stinks,
then tell me if you
think it's a better idea
to sacrifice the Earth for
another planet's safety?
(ship rumbling)
(wind howling)
- [Tochiro] Hmm?
- I am Emeraldas, a
freelance space trader,
and I hold a legitimate license.
I am no one's enemy and no one's ally.
I'm a free space trader.
Who are you?
- [Tochiro] My name is Tochiro.
- And what do you want?
- I'm looking for my friend.
But your ship, she's
scorched pretty badly.
- [Emeraldas] I made an error in crossing
the Flame Stream Prominence.
It's called the Owen
Stanley Witch of Space.
Not only is there tremendous heat energy,
but super gravitation that
pulls in any life reaction.
(wind howling)
(panting)
- [La Mime] Zoll.
(gasping)
- What's wrong La Mime?
It's dangerous to come here.
- [La Mime] I know that, but--
- Tell me what's wrong?
- [La Mime] I heard the
top secret coded order
sent to the general commander.
- Ah?
- Hmm?
- [La Mime] It's Torkarga.
- What about it?
- [La Mime] They're going to...
- [Maya On Radio] No matter how great
the bitter agony may be
consider it as the sigh
of the beautiful future yet to come.
Do not let despair lure you to defeat.
The crisp air at dawn, the
fresh wind, remember it all.
Remember the time we ran hand and hand
over the green, green fields,
remember with love, remember.
(dramatic music)
(panting)
(suspenseful music)
(guns firing)
(yelling)
(thumping)
(groaning)
(gun firing)
(yelling)
(guns firing)
- Harlock.
- Maya, look out, take cover.
Maya.
Maya!
(guns firing)
(yelling)
- Harlock!
- Maya.
Maya.
(gun firing)
(dramatic music)
Maya.
(gun firing)
(groaning)
- Harlock.
No.
Don't come closer.
Your coming this far,
it's more than enough to make me happy.
Hurry and get away.
- How can I leave without you?
- Oh no.
Don't come any closer.
Don't, don't throw your life away.
(groaning)
Stay alive and someday I
know we'll be together again.
Harlock, please don't.
Don't come any closer.
Harlock.
(dramatic music)
Please don't. (crying)
- [Man] Fire!
- [Phantom] Maya!
(strained breathing)
- Harlock, what's wrong?
- A little man called Tochiro,
have you seen him around here?
- [Tochiro] Hey, you finally came.
- [Emeraldas] And just
where have you been hiding?
- [Tochiro] I've been repairing the ship.
I still need one part to make it perfect,
but even without it she's ready to fly.
- [Phantom] You mean you
fixed it, it's ready to go?
- [Tochiro] Don't you believe me?
- It's not that, can she fly?
- She sure can.
Hey why don't you come aboard and see?
(groaning)
- Harlock.
Harlock, what's wrong?
(unsettling music)
- [Maya On Radio] This is
the voice of Free Arcadia.
If you let it burn only ashes will remain,
but a true living fire of
hope will never die out.
Some day like a forest fire it will spread
from one to the other increasing its power
and that hope will create
a new and beautiful future.
Even if you set off
tomorrow to a distant place
no one will think badly of you
for people do have faith in
you that you will return.
(glass cracking)
(gasping)
(suspenseful music)
- [Tochiro] She's been captured.
- I can almost picture that poor girl.
In her heart she's not
only holding the torch
for her oppressed people,
but she seems to be in love
with a particular person.
That broadcast we just heard
must've been a personal message.
She put her life in danger to
send that message to someone.
- Emeraldas.
Would you do me a favor
and let me steal your ship?
- [Tochiro] What did you say?
- Because I must escape from Earth.
- [Zoll] I can't let you do that.
- You're just as rotten
as the rest of them.
You've turned yourself
into a Illumidus dog.
- [La Mime] Harlock, wait a moment.
Zoll didn't come here to arrest you.
We've come to take over Emeraldas' ship.
Our people want to go back to Torkarga.
- That's enough La Mime.
They've got nothing to do with this.
- Oh?
- [La Mime] My planet was
totally destroyed by Illumidus
and reverted to a primitive state.
The sight I saw from the refugee ship.
I can never forget the grief I felt
when our planet lost its glow.
And now Zoll and all the
other Torkarga people
are facing the same tragedy.
If Zoll and the others escape
Illumidus will retaliate.
Still they're driven by their
love for their mother planet.
If destruction is inevitable they want
to perish on Torkarga with their families.
They need a ship to return to Torkarga
and that's why we've come.
(dramatic music)
The same thing will
happen to Earth some day.
For now I beg of you, let
Zoll and the others go.
- I'm sorry for what I've said.
I understand.
- [Murigson] All our forces
have taken emergency positions.
- Hmm, I have been overlooking
those underground broadcasts
so far thinking it would give
the Earthmen a will to work.
- Yes, but I thought today's broadcast
sounded like a message to start
a full scale revolt here on Earth
or possibly urging them to escape.
- Don't worry they can't go anywhere.
They're like rats in a cage making
a lot of noise, but they can't escape.
- If Tochiro hadn't repaired my ship
it would've been abandoned,
therefor take it.
- [Tochiro] Wait, if you use this ship
no matter what she says
Emeraldas will lose
her free space traders license.
Also as soon as Zoll takes off
they will immediately
commence to attack Torkarga.
So we'll use another ship.
Harlock, let us go to Torkarga
in place of Zoll and the others.
I've been waiting a long
time, such a long time.
Struggling to stay alive,
living like a beggar.
I've been waiting for this chance.
Waiting for the day when I
could set out in my own spaceship.
- In your own spaceship?
- [Tochiro] I've been
looking for a captain
worthy enough to entrust
him with my spaceship.
- This spaceship, where is it?
(laughing)
- I got one, I've got one. (laughing)
- Your, you really are incredible.
- Zoll, what do you say?
With their spaceship and with
their help perhaps we could--
- No this is strictly a Torkarga problem.
Just let us have the use of the ship.
- [Tochiro] No I can't let you do that.
The ship is me, every bit of it is me
and it won't move without me.
- [La Mime] Zoll let me go in your place.
Please, and ask Harlock and
Tochiro to go to Torkarga.
In return you stay here
and pretend loyalty
to Illumidus and protect the Earthmen.
Illumidus is much too strong as an enemy.
The only way to ruin them is
to take invisible measures
like bacteria spoiling it from inside.
- You want me to be the
bacteria here on Earth?
- [La Mime] Yes.
- And we'll be the bacteria on Torkarga.
- Zoll I will go with them on the ship
as a delegate of Torkarga
and you take over here.
- I've been a dog, a dog begging
for the lives of my people,
a dog that fights as
instrument of Illumidus.
The people who remained on Torkarga
have been dreaming of
a day of deliverance.
Believing that we will come
back to rescue them some day
as they hold their breath
under Illumidus's oppression.
When I close my eyes I
can see my little brother
and sister praying and
waiting for my return
bearing so much bitterness and yet
praying for me to come back and save them.
(dramatic music)
Tochiro hurry to Torkarga.
(crying)
I am grateful to you for
making all this possible.
Thank you.
(crying)
(dramatic music)
- Now for the future of Torkarga
and to the men of true courage,
Zoll of Torkaraga, for
Harlock, Tochiro and La Mime
and all the rest of you brave men.
(speaking in a foreign language)
- [La Mime] It's a Torkargan word
to toast with true friends.
It means we pledge true
friendship with our blood.
(speaking in a foreign language)
(guns firing)
(yelling)
(wind howling)
- Take this to Harlock, please hurry.
(coughing)
(suspenseful music)
(guns firing)
(yelling)
- Interesting, let's see
just how far they can go.
- [Man] Maya sent this.
She made it especially for
you and asked that you use it.
- [Tochiro] Harlock we've got to hurry.
- Don't worry, we'll protect Maya.
Farewell and I wish you a successful trip.
- Harlock.
(suspenseful music)
Down here.
- Maya, you shouldn't be up.
- I haven't got too much longer to live
so please let me see Harlock take off.
- [Tochiro] And this, the
ship I built to fulfill
our ancestor's dream
and I named her Arcadia.
- Arcadia?
- Only the name Arcadia would be suitable
for a ship that we launch.
- Arcadia.
- And this is our ship.
Our own ship.
And you built this?
- That's right.
A ship I built with the technology
I inherited from my ancestors.
It took a long time, but Harlock
this is the ship to achieve our dream.
(dramatic music)
What's that?
It's fantastic.
Do you want to go and see Maya?
- She wouldn't want me to do that.
She'd be upset.
- But...
- With this flag flying
from the mast we'll leave.
- [Murigson] The rebellious
Earthmen are being put under
our control but we can't
find Harlock anywhere.
- Anyway he's like a rat in a trap.
(rumbling)
What?
- Launching angle 40 degrees.
Balance normal.
Release all circuit seals.
Release armament safety circuit.
Cylinder exercitation rate
360 million per second.
All systems normal.
Release thrust conductor valve.
Energize artificial gravity.
Activate rifle radar.
Throttle slow to full speed ahead.
(rumbling)
- [Phantom] Arcadia, lift off.
(tense music)
(yelling)
(screaming)
- Where the devil did that come from?
(upbeat rock music)
♪ I'll never be content with sorrow ♪
♪ Or thoughts of yesterday ♪
♪ I'll spread my wings to meet tomorrow ♪
♪ And then we fly away ♪
♪ Our life's too short
to spend it waiting ♪
♪ For time to take its toll ♪
♪ Instead I'll spend it celebrating ♪
♪ The freedom of my soul ♪
(gasping)
♪ To be free without a care ♪
♪ To live a life no matter where ♪
♪ To truly see and be aware ♪
♪ Take on whatever's there ♪
♪ Though there are times
when it's so hard ♪
♪ To face it alone ♪
♪ But when the shadows fade away ♪
♪ I'll be here to see the brand new day ♪
Stop that ship.
Stop that ship immediately!
(electronic buzzing)
- That's the Illumidus
Occupation Force radio.
(gasping)
Emeraldas.
- [La Mime] Maya.
- By six a.m. Earth time tomorrow
if you do not return
to Earth and surrender
these two female rebels
will be publicly executed.
- Why the--
- To prevent another uprising
from happening again.
They will be executed by a firing
squad at the crack of dawn.
- [Tochiro] No!
- [La Mime] We must go back.
We can't let them be sacrificed.
- An execution will definitely
provoke the Earthmen to revolt.
That spaceship is not coming back.
They've abandoned those two women
and that's enough for
us to use as propaganda.
- Just the opposite.
We've got to set an example
otherwise the rebels
will get more aggressive.
- If you cancel the execution
I cannot guarantee we'll have full control
over the Earthmen anymore.
(birds squawking)
(wind howling)
- Earthmen executing Earthmen?
They've turned into Illumidus dogs.
(dramatic music)
- Are they really going to do it?
- After all, the spaceship did not return.
(laughing)
it seems your friends have abandoned you.
- The entire proceedings of this execution
are being transmitted to
your friends' spaceship.
This will be your last
chance to plead with them.
Ask them to return and save you.
- Sorry to disappoint you,
but neither of us is going to do that.
Harlock and the others
wouldn't return anyway.
- It bois down to the fact
that they are nothing
but a bunch of cowards.
- You wouldn't know the
real meaning of being brave.
You're just an ignorant alien
who knows nothing about Earthmen.
- What?
(slap thwacking)
(gasping)
You may proceed.
- Ready.
(guns cocking)
- Harlock.
(suspenseful music)
- Fire.
(guns firing)
(birds squawking)
(shouting)
- Stop them.
- Fire, fire, fire.
- Fire!
(shouting)
(guns firing)
Stop them!
- They'll pay for this.
(guns firing)
- [Man] The Earthmen and
the Torkarga soldiers
revolted and Zoll is leading the men.
(guns firing)
- Stay back, stay back.
(gun firing)
(gasping)
- Maya.
(gun firing)
(gasping)
(whimpering)
- Farewell my friends.
Forgive me for not protecting
them as I promised.
(dramatic music)
- [Phantom] Tochiro raise the flag.
- [Tochiro] Raise the flag?
- [Phantom] Yes.
Raise our flag.
- [Tochiro] Alright.
(orchestral music)
- [Phantom] Set Arcadia's
course for planet Torkarga.
Zoll I'll keep our promise.
(orchestral music)
- Maya.
- Emeraldas please forgive me
for thinking only of Harlock.
That's the only reason I used the radio,
to urge him to escape
from this terrible place
and my doing it caused the death of Zoll
and caused your beautiful
face to be scarred for life
and so many people have
been hurt and captured.
All this happened because
of my broadcasting.
I am the one who should be executed.
- That's not true.
Even without your radio sooner or later
all the people of Earth,
even Zoll and me would've done this.
I'm sure Harlock, Tochiro and La Mime
would also have done the same.
- This is Illumidus Fleet Command.
All ships will proceed
to Earth immediately
as reinforcement for
Earth occupation troops.
- [Zeda] Reinforcements
for one man like Harlock?
Murigson.
- [Murigson] Yes?
- I am positive Harlock will return
and you'd better start thinking up a plan
of how we're going to handle it.
- [Murigson] Yes sir.
- That's the planet Torkarga.
- [La Mime] That's the
planet Zoll told me about.
It used to be a beautiful
planet with rich green forests.
(eerie music)
- Hmm, my home and now it's been
almost completely destroyed.
(suspenseful music)
That just shows you what
Illumidus can do to a planet.
The monsters.
- [Phantom] It looks like the planet
has already been annihilated.
But lets go down and have a look.
(dramatic music)
(thunder booming)
(blast booming)
- [La Mime] Everything is destroyed.
There's not a single life reaction.
Torkarga is finished.
- Huh?
Drones.
(guns firing)
(explosions booming)
There's an automated defense system.
(gun firing)
(groaning)
(guns firing)
(dramatic music)
They must've fought till the last man.
And I don't know where to start looking
for Zoll's sister and brother.
- Brother Zoll come back to
Torkarga, please save us.
Brother Zoll come back to
(rumbling)
(gun firing)
(explosion booming)
- Hey.
- Hey!
(laughing)
(cheering)
- Why you're still alive.
You really are alive.
(laughing)
I'm so glad. (laughing)
Yes I'm so glad to find
someone still alive.
- Brother Zoll come back to
Torkarga, please save us.
- [La Mime] What a dreadful thing.
They even burnt women and children.
- And the Earth will be next.
- Please save us.
(gun firing)
(explosion booming)
Brother Zoll come back to
Torkarga, please save us.
- Brother Zoll.
Brother Zoll please help me. (groaning)
- [La Mime] Mira.
- You've come back.
Please help me.
- Harlock, hurry and come back.
There's a planet demolition bomb
right under the tower.
(bomb whistling)
(explosion booming)
- Huh?
Take care of Mira.
- Harlock do you hear me?
We must evacuate at once.
What's the matter with them?
Why don't they come back?
- What is the situation on the surface?
- We've got a big problem.
A planet demolition bomb is set
right at Harlock's position.
- A bomb?
The Illumidus fleet.
- All ships 45 degrees to port
and cover all possible escape routes
of the enemy spaceship.
- [Tochiro] Harlock, La
Mime, return at once.
- [Phantom] Arcadia lift off.
Full speed gravity break away.
(dramatic music)
(whimpering)
(explosion booming)
(gasping)
- Brother Zoll please
save Torkarga, please.
(dramatic music)
- If we keep on this course
we'll collide with the Illumidus fleet.
- [Phantom] Can we lose them?
- It's possible if we change course
but then we'll be forced to go across
the deadly Flame Stream Prominence.
- The Owen Stanley Witch of Space.
- That's right.
The five fire streams that go
over the double sun, Besberas.
The hardest part of space
where Emeraldas ship was scorched.
- Alright we'll do exactly
what my ancestor did.
Change course and we'll challenge
the Owen Stanley Witch of space.
(flames crackling)
(dramatic music)
(gasping)
- Our ship's heat resistance is higher
than that of Emeraldas's ship,
but she told me that the stream feeds
off of life reaction.
Thrust decrease 70%.
Our defense speed is plus four.
We're being pulled into
the river of flame.
- She's laughing.
The witch is laughing at us.
(echoing laughing)
- Save me please.
- [La Mime] It's alright Mira,
you'll see Zoll pretty soon.
- Big brother Zoll I held
out as long as I could.
(gasping)
(dramatic music)
- Now listen to me.
The last Torkarga female has just died.
Now there is no one left
to bear Torkarga children.
The Torkarga race is now
doomed to extinction.
Never forget that Harlock and the others
risked their lives to try
and give Torkarga a future.
- Thrust minus 80%, descent speed plus 10.
We're descending too fast.
- Tochiro maximum thrust, all engines.
(flames crackling)
- Come on.
(echoing laughing)
Hey we've started gaining thrust.
(laughing)
Harlock we did it.
We beat the Owen Stanley Witch of Space.
(flames crackling)
Oh, Mira.
- [La Mime] It's not only Mira who died.
- What?
(footsteps rapidly thudding)
(dramatic music)
(gasping)
- [La Mime] To cancel
out the life reaction
which was pulling the ship down.
- Everyone of them jumped
out into the river of flames?
(flames crackling)
(dramatic music)
(orchestral music)
- What, Harlock is coming back?
Never.
I'll alert the fleet.
Intercept that ship.
- [Zeda] Hold it.
Let him return safely to Earth.
- But why?
It's only one ship, let's shoot it down.
- Yes it's only one ship,
but are we going to mobilize
our entire fleet to shoot it down?
It will only make the
Earthmen revolt again.
(groaning)
- [Murigson] Commander
we must intercept it.
- They have formally
requested permission to land.
To send out our force to
shoot down a spaceship
with people who voluntarily
wish to return to this planet
where only misery awaits them
is something I cannot do.
They are very brave people
and it's time we showed
them a little respect.
- Maya Harlock is coming
back to the Earth.
(gasping)
He even made a formal
request to Commander Zeda
for permission to land here.
- He's coming back to Earth
and he'll only suffer again.
- I knew he would come back.
That's the kind of man he is.
The next time when his spaceship
leaves Earth let's go with him.
You've already done more
than enough here on Earth.
- [Maya On Radio] This is
the voice of Free Arcadia
broadcasting on a new frequency,
variable microwave 8390.
8390.
This is the voice of Free Arcadia
holding flowers in our hands.
Let's proceed to the desert
and welcome home our hope
for the future with flowers.
(dramatic music)
- [La Mime] Zoll.
- Zoll, I came back as I promised I would,
but I came back too late, forgive me.
I brought your sister Mira back with us.
- Come back to Torkarga, please save us.
Brother Zoll come back to
Torkarga, please save us.
- [Triter] You came all the way back here
just to say that to a dead man
even though you knew
we'd be waiting for you?
You're nothing but a stupid fool.
- If you don't understand
I feel sorry for you.
- Maybe what you've
done made you feel good,
but it puts Earth in a
very difficult position.
At present Earth has an agreement
to maintain cooperative
relations with Illumidus
even though some idiots
are planning a revolt
they will soon be suppressed.
We want to maintain peace on Earth
and a dangerous element like you
does not fit in with our present policy
and therefore our government orders you
to be permanently exiled from Earth.
- What's that?
- If you insist on remaining here on Earth
we will have no other course,
but to order our forces to fight you.
- You want to fight against us?
- You happen to be enemies of Earth.
- Enemies of Earth?
Alright, if you say we're not
welcome here than we shall leave.
- But Harlock.
- Harlock is right.
There's no need for anyone to stay here
and lower himself to the
level of being a pig.
- Emeraldas.
Emeraldas.
(dramatic music)
- The two of you there
listen very carefully,
the savageness of Murigson
who shot Maya and me
will long be remembered.
And the coward traitor who shot Zoll
will never be forgiven.
The ruthlessness of you two
who think nothing of the
life of man shall be avenged.
- But I was--
- Don't bother making excuses.
You can never justify what you have done.
- This is the voice of Free Arcadia.
This is Maya.
My dear Earthmen I wish to continue
to stay on the air and be with you.
Oh, I wanted to continue being with you.
But now I cannot keep going on.
Please forgive me.
This is the last voice of Free Arcadia.
- Maya.
- This is--
- Maya, that's enough.
It's alright.
- Harlock I had faith in you.
I knew in my heart that
you would come back again.
I knew that you would keep your promise
even though your friend
Zoll is no longer with us.
- We'll go together to the Sea of Stars.
- I've been dreaming all these
years of a beautiful place.
We used to play together
and now I will saail
in the Arcadia with you
over the Sea of Stars.
- Maya.
Maya.
Why did you leave me?
I had so many things to say.
Maya.
(dramatic music)
- Everyone, Maya who kept
appealing to all of you
to believe in a better
future for Earth is now gone
and the government of Earth has just
condemned all of us to permanent exile.
All of you beware, for
the Earth will become
a second Torkarga and how
will you survive that?
I urge all of you all of you
to remember the voice of Free Arcadia.
- That's enough Tochiro.
Since we've been exiled
we better leave now.
Under that flag is there anyone
among you who wants to join us?
(dramatic music)
Under that flag, do you pledge to fight
for those who believe in freedom?
- I do.
- You can never return.
- The Sea of Stars will be
our home, our only home.
(tense music)
- Let's go.
- Keep your filthy hands off.
He was my best friend.
- Hold it Harlock.
I am also a proud man and if you wish
to depart safely you
must first go through me.
- A duel?
- Yes.
And the choice of weapons
and the place shall be mine.
By custom a duel is fought one to one
and I forbid interference.
- Very well.
- Commander you can't let
that man get away now.
(grunting)
(suspenseful music)
- You object to my decision
and you raise a weapon in defiance of me
and let that be the end of you.
(gun firing)
- [Maya] Now my loved one sets out
with the flag of our freedom.
Farewell until the day
you come back to me.
I believe in you.
No matter how far apart we may be
I know that you will
never forget the Earth.
(dramatic music)
No one can keep you from leaving
with your flag floating high.
Farewell my Harlock.
You always had faith and hope in tomorrow
no matter what the circumstances.
And I am proud to have shared
my days in the past with you.
I pray that your future will
be the one you believe in.
Farewell my dear Harlock.
Live on with hope.
Live forever.
I see it so clearly deep inside
your heart the flame is burning,
believing in your future.
The fire of the man who will
never betray his friends.
I love you and I will be apart
of the flame in your heart.
Deep in you heart I will
be with you forever.
(dramatic music)
- [Emeraldas] Harlock.
Look at the red pirate flag on my ship.
It's the color of Maya's blood.
Maya's white dress dyed like her blood,
the flag of a pirate.
The red badge of freedom
that man is seeking.
The flag of my freedom.
- Maya was Harlock's--
- That's right the kind of woman
who never tired down the one she loved.
The kind of woman even you
would've fallen in love with.
(dramatic music)
- Ah?
It's signaling follow me.
That's the Illumidus flag ship.
- Harlock, I've found
a true Earthman in you
that no computer could fathom
and Tochiro came out
the same and also Maya.
Therefore not as commander
of the Earth Occupation Force
but as man to man I am determined
to have a duel with you.
And I hope you will
fight without restraint.
- [Woman] Contact report.
The Illumidus fleet
attack force of 624 ships.
(gasping)
- I think Commander Zeda
is trying to pull us away
in the opposite direction
from the area the Illumidus
fleet is approaching.
- Increase our thrust.
- Roger.
We're closing fast on the enemy ship.
- Take combat positions.
Combat speed five.
All turrets combat ready.
(orchestral music)
Open all reverse jets and accelerate.
- [Tochiro] Roger, reduce
to combat speed three.
- Port side gunner
aligned, stand by to fire.
Fire at 0.1 garm intervals.
30 micro-garms before volley.
- Relative velocity, 128,000.
Altitude variance zero.
Main gun tracking speed in sync.
10 seconds before discharge.
Eight, seven, six, five,
four, three, two, one.
- Fire.
(guns firing)
(yelling)
(explosions booming)
- Port side aft dispatch
damage control team.
(guns firing)
- Give me a damage assessment report.
- [Woman] Port launching tube disabled.
- [Man] Port exhaust valve damaged.
- Number 16 hold and the rear
of the airship have been hit.
- [Phantom] Hard to port, 180 degrees.
- Reduce speed and hard to starboard, 180.
(dramatic music)
Vertical angle, vector octave.
Range six million vols.
Synchronize all starboard turrets.
(orchestral music)
Fire.
- Fire.
(guns firing)
(yelling)
- [Man] Port side guns disabled.
(dramatic music)
- Tochiro are you alright?
- I'm alright, but see that?
The automatic firing
sight, it's been destroyed.
(suspenseful music)
- Transfer all personnel
from the side pod hull
to the center master control ship at once.
I repeat, transfer all
personnel from the side pod hull
to the center master control ship at once.
- You've got the answer?
- Yes.
A manual sight, it's right in here.
- A manual sight.
- Look.
- Why that's--
- Yes, the original sight your
ancestor gave to my ancestor.
(dramatic music)
- And this, it's what tied our
ancestors together, the eye.
- Our eye.
(dramatic music)
- [Phantom] Here he comes.
- Roger.
Maintain course and speed.
- Eject both of the side pod
hulls and full combat speed.
(gasping)
- [La Mime] And Zeda's center
control ship hasn't been damaged.
- [Phantom] Concentrate
fire on the central bridge.
- I hope this sight is going to work.
- Tochiro open fire.
- Roger.
(guns firing)
(laughing)
- That's it Tochiro, give him a broadside.
(guns firing)
(screaming)
(explosions booming)
- Keep firing.
(guns firing)
- You alright Tochiro?
- I'm still alive I guess,
but if they come back and attack
us one more time forget it.
(explosion booming)
(screaming)
- All personnel abandon ship.
(dramatic music)
- [Phantom] Zeda's turning back
for another frontal attack.
- And I can't guarantee
what'll happen this time.
He's coming directly at us.
- Zeda is a brave man.
Years ago there used to be a lot
of brave men like him on Earth.
- He's going to hit us head on.
This is it, here goes.
- Tochiro, hold your fire.
- Harlock you fought very well.
When we meet in hell let's
have a drink together.
Till then guard your life
and keep living and fighting
to accomplish that long
cherished dream of yours.
Now farewell.
(gasping)
(dramatic music)
(explosion booming)
(yelling)
- [Phantom] Farewell Zeda,
I'll meet you in hell.
- Harlock.
Commander Zeda led us to a position
where we can escape from
the Illumidus fleet,
but only if we reverse
course now and accelerate.
- This is our new start on life.
I'd hate to be called a coward
who turned and ran after his first battle.
Tochiro what do you think about it?
- Well I don't want to
show my back to the enemy.
- I can see that anyone who goes
against you is in for trouble.
- A pirate must live a pirate's life
and this is the way of
life we have chosen.
Action stations.
Full speed ahead, prepare for combat.
(orchestral music)
- He's trying to escape.
All ships fly in point,
open fire with energy bolts
and destroy that pirate ship.
(guns firing)
- [Man] Captain, all advanced ships report
that their energy bolts
failed to go straight.
Computer side estimation
readouts are all wrong.
- What?
- [Tochiro] Harlock, the magnetic field
and dimension wave around us
are showing an extraordinary phenomenon.
- [Phantom] What's that mean?
- It looks normal to the naked eye,
but the instruments can't read
the exact position of the enemy ships.
- The explosion of Zeda's
ship must've done it.
When his high powered engines blew up
they must've warped space
over a very large area
and I'll bet he did it
intentionally just to protect us.
Alright, frontal attack.
We'll board their flagship.
(guns firing)
- Don't stop, keep on firing.
(orchestral music)
(gasping)
This is no way to fight.
- It isn't in the rule book, too bad
because this is a pirate's way to fight.
(gun firing)
(groaning)
(yelling)
(gun firing)
This is a lesson to teach you
to sheer off when you see my flag.
(air whooshing)
(screaming)
Both engines, full break away speed.
And set a course for the Sea of Stars.
(explosions booming)
(dramatic music)
Whatever the spirit is that
governs the universe and space
let my friend Zoll and Mira the last
Torkarga female return to your bosom.
Now let Zoll and Mira
rest in peace forever.
- Farewell my friends.
(dramatic music)
- [Phantom] Somewhere at the
point where the rings of time
come in contact we shall meet again.
Goodbye Maya.
Till the last moment of my
life in the Sea of Stars
the memory of you will stay with me.
- [Tochiro] Ready Harlock?
(dramatic music)
- The Sea of Stars, we submit
our loved ones into your hands.
(dramatic music)
We will never surrender to anyone.
We will never seek help from others.
We will never fight under any other flag
and we will fight only
for what we believe in.
Standing under our own flag
we shall continue to fight for as long
as we live under this flag of freedom.
Our ship of freedom Arcadia, lift off!
- Queen Emeraldas lift off.
(upbeat rock music)
♪ I'll never be content with sorrow ♪
♪ Or thoughts of yesterday ♪
♪ I'll spread my wings to meet tomorrow ♪
♪ And then we fly away. ♪
♪ A life's too short to spend it waiting ♪
♪ For time to take its toll ♪
♪ Instead I'll spend it celebrating ♪
♪ The freedom of my soul ♪
- Attention all citizens of
Earth the rebels are gone.
Now let us proceed to work hard
to create a paradise on Earth
in cooperation with
Illumidus and we will--
- [Phantom Thnking] Fool that
you are, dance all you want
in your small world to
your heart's content.
The world we have is the whole
universe of unlimited space.
(upbeat music)
♪ The road I walk may be of gravel ♪
♪ Quite a bit of stone ♪
♪ But I know every day I travel ♪
♪ My future is my own ♪
♪ So here's goodbye to all the sorrow ♪
♪ That caused yesterday ♪
♪ I'm on my way to meet tomorrow ♪
♪ Solitude's a price I'll pay ♪
♪ To be free without a care ♪
♪ To live a life no matter where ♪
♪ To truly see and be aware ♪
♪ Take on whatever's there ♪
♪ Oh there were times when it was hard ♪
♪ To face the night alone ♪
♪ But now the darkness fades away ♪
♪ And here I stand to
greet the brand new day ♪
♪ To be free without a care ♪
♪ To live a life no matter where ♪
♪ To truly see and be aware ♪
♪ Take on whatever's there ♪
♪ Oh there were times when it was hard ♪
♪ To face the night alone ♪
♪ But now the darkness fades away ♪
♪ And here I stand to
greet the brand new day ♪
(engine rumbling)