[ASIRPA]
Right now,
Huci is probably
out in the field,
harvesting grain.
[geese quacking]
The flocks of wild geese
in the skies are a sign
that the salmon,
which bring the Ainu life,
are on their way up the river.
The name we have
for the salmon is "kamuycep."
Meaning "the fish of the gods."
Or "sipe," Which means
"real food," more or less.
♪
See those?
Get some down for me.
They're "kutci," kiwi berries.
[SUGIMOTO]
Mm.
Holy. This thing is delicious.
It's so sweet.
[ASIRPA]
If you eat too much kutci,
your anus starts to itch.
Eat up, Sugimoto.
The eastern Ainu call
wild berries "salmon berries,"
because when they turn red,
it's time for the salmon
to come up the river.
Sounds like a nice time of year.
Having both these and salmon
to look forward to at once.
[ASIRPA]
Look, Sugimoto,
a bear made that with its claw.
This time of year, the bears eat
nothing but those kiwi berries.
Because of that,
sometimes their meat
will even taste like kutci.
[SUGIMOTO]
Sometimes I'm amazed
at all the things
you know, Asirpa.
[ASIRPA]
My aca.
He's the one
who taught me everything.
About the mountains.
The Ainu. Everything.
-Sugimoto.
-Huh?
I'm scared. Help me.
If I learn my father killed
and stole from the Ainu,
it would break my heart.
What do I do?
You should meet him.
We've already gotten
this far, right?
Hey, no matter what,
I'm with you till the end.
♪
[SUGIMOTO]
So, as you all know,
Abashiri Prison
is surrounded by mountains.
And there are
several dozen posts
with armed guards.
The sides facing the mountains
are well guarded
because that's where
the prisoners are kept.
But that's the least
of their worries.
They're far less concerned
about escapees
than about people
coming to take Nopperabo.
[SHIRAISHI]
Which is why I was saying
we'll need to go
through the wall
on the Abashiri side,
where it's not as well-guarded.
Here.
♪
[SHIRAISHI] We can only
pull this plan off now,
while the salmon
are spawning.
We'll use an Ainu hut as a cover
to hide the tunnel entrance.
Huh?
[gasps]
[KADOKURA]
What the hell is this?
-Huh?
-Hmm.
[KADOKURA]
You can't build this thing here.
Somebody's up there.
I want this taken down, now.
Why in the world
would you want to set it up
right in this spot, anyway?
♪
[TANIGAKI] So you're saying
you want more salmon?
[KADOKURA]
Oh...
What do you mean?
We made a deal with your men.
We all agreed on
three salmon a day
for the right to fish here.
Go ahead, ask your guards there.
[shudders]
You dishonor the uniform
accepting bribes.
[SOLDIERS sigh]
[sighs deeply]
Fisherman, make it five.
Or the hut comes down,
you got it?
We'd be better off
just letting the foxes get them.
Chief Kadokura,
please don't tell Warden Inudou
about this, okay?
[KADOKURA]
Of course not, you idiot.
[sighs]
Hmm?
♪
[ASIRPA] Salmon used to be
the Ainu's primary food source.
In years when there were
very few salmon,
people actually starved.
So we never waste things.
We've learned to make use
of every part of the fish.
First of all,
you chop off the head.
Then cut out the cartilage
called "hizu,"
it's in the middle
of the upper jaw.
There's a dish
you can make with that.
Sugimoto, can you guess
what it is?
Staying calm.
I think I might know what it is.
I really do.
[ASIRPA]
Chitatap!
Did you hear that?!
We're having chitatap!
So originally,
"chitatap" referred
to the kind made from salmon.
It's the father
of all chitataps!
Ow! Stop grabbing me.
[ASIRPA] You make it
from the gills and hizu.
The more you mince it,
the better it gets.
Chitatap, chitatap,
chitatap, chitatap.
Can I use this to make chitatap?
[gasps]
Chitatap, chitatap.
Chitatap, chitatap, chitatap.
Ogata.
Everybody else is saying it.
If you're not even willing
to say this one word with us,
how are we supposed to feel?
I had really been hoping
that this might bring
everyone together.
-Chitatap.
-Hmm?
He said it! Did you hear him?
Ogata just said "chitatap,"
you guys!
Was I really the only one
who heard it?
♪
We prepare a couple of dishes
with the roe,
mixed with porridge,
it's "chiporosayo."
Mixed with potatoes,
it's "cipor rataskep."
Mm. Mm.
It's soft and easy to chew.
So this is
the real chitatap, huh?
This fish is so fresh,
it doesn't even smell.
Hinna, hinna.
This is great.
Really crisp and juicy.
Your name is Inkarmat,
is that right?
So, got yourself a man?
[grunts]
Hey.
[CIKIAPASI]
Here.
What do you think you're doing?
That's mine.
If a girl makes a boy a meal
at his house,
and he eats half of it,
but then he gives it back
to her to finish,
once she eats
the rest of his food.
they're officially betrothed.
So that was basically
an Ainu proposal.
Yeah. Why not be a real family?
Oh! Such tension.
I could watch this all day.
Cikapasi, give that back.
Hmm?
Uh-oh.
Guess they're still
in that delicate stage, huh?
[groans]
[INKARMAT]
Tanigaki Nispa.
I saw you watching the prison
from the other side
of the river.
You say you don't believe
Nopperabo is Wilk.
But I think you came here
because part of you
hopes that he is.
You're absolutely right.
Before I met him,
I'd been wandering through life
alone as an orphan.
The time I spent with him
was beautiful.
It does still have a hold on me.
But my fortune-telling
has been clear.
We'll never meet
in this life again.
But every time another fortune
came true,
my desire to see him
only grew stronger.
And then,
I heard of his death.
It was impossible.
I'd always believed
it would be my own death
that kept us from meeting again.
That's what my fortune had said.
Then, when I looked
into how he had died,
I met Lieutenant Tsurumi,
who said he had Wilk's things.
Wilk was dead.
[inaudible]
[INKARMAT] Nopperabo in Abashiri
knew the location
of the stolen gold
and was working
with Kiroranke.
That's what he told me.
I assumed my fortune-telling
must've been wrong.
I reconciled myself to that.
But then, when I was
drowning in the lake,
I felt it.
I truly was destined
to die that day.
But you, you changed the fate
my fortune-telling
laid out for me.
I learned that day,
one's fate can be changed.
I know this may not make
a lot of sense to you.
But for the moment, I have hope.
That one day soon, I might
actually see Wilk again.
But please understand,
it's not a desire to see
someone that I love.
It's more of a fervent wish
to free myself from my past.
You know why?
Because I want to look
to the future with you.
♪
I still have a job I need to do.
Bringing Asirpa
safely back to Huci.
When that's done,
then I promise,
if you make me a bowl of food,
I'll only eat half.
Would you stop?
That food belongs to
Tanigaki Nispa, not you.
[SUGIMOTO] Hey, Kiroranke,
where does this come out?
You sure it's safe?
[KIRORANKE] We dug the exact
distance Hijikata told us to.
We'll have to trust him.
I'm just saying,
if we poke our heads
into the guards' mess hall,
we're screwed.
Uh...
♪
[gasps]
It's about time.
You're in the right place.
[SUGIMOTO]
Uh...
Where's that?
[KADOKURA]
My lodgings.
♪
Warden Inudou's orders are firm.
Nopperabo is moved
to a different cell every day.
But that's where I come in, see?
I can tell you
where they're going to move him.
On the night
of the next full moon,
Nopperabo will be taken
to this unit right here.
Building four. Cell number 66.
So the goal is to break in
and get Asirpa
in front of Nopperabo.
If we can manage to do that
and leave without a trace,
we win.
If we fail, they find the tunnel
and Kadokura's a wanted man.
That seems like a pretty
big risk for you to take.
Well, if that happens,
I'm with you, Hijikata.
See, before my father died,
he fought with
the old shogunate,
right alongside you.
He'd be happy to see me
follow you.
Hmm.
What if we discover
that Nopperabo
is Asirpa's father.
How hard will it be
to get him out?
He's had one of his
Achilles tendons cut,
so it will be difficult,
but not impossible.
There's no need to take the risk
of getting him out.
If my father really
is Nopperabo...
Hmph.
You might as well stop
hiding down there and join us.
Heard about you.
Hyakunosuke Ogata,
the illegitimate son
of the Seventh Division's
former leader and his mistress.
For somebody
who just deserted
in order to track down
the gold for himself,
you have
a complicated backstory.
Ah.
Like hell have I ever wanted
my father's career.
What a pain in the ass
that would be.
And anyway, heh,
don't pretend like you guys
can trust each other
any more than you do me.
[SHIRAISHI]
Hey, I just had a thought.
Have you ever tried
using your fortune-telling
to see who Nopperabo is?
Yes, I have, many times.
Why would you do it
more than once?
[INKARMAT] At first, the answer
was always no,
he was not Asirpa's father.
But the more I ask the question,
the more that's begun to change.
It's starting to become clear.
The yeses are catching up.
So now, which side is winning?
I just did it a while ago.
Out of a thousand tries,
I got the five hundredth yes.
Well, then,
what if you did it one last time
to break the tie?
♪
[grunts]
What are you doing?
[SHIRAISHI]
Never mind. Don't do it.
This isn't going to help us now.
What we need,
is to go find out for ourselves.
[NARRATOR] And on a black,
moonless night...
[SUGIMOTO] Inkarmat, Cikapasi,
Nagakura, and Ienaga,
you'll stay in the kotan.
Ogata, hide in the mountains.
A little rifle support
if we need it.
Tanigaki, you'll stand by with
the log rafts we hid riverside.
Kiroranke, Ushiyama,
and Hijikata,
stand by in the lodging house.
Shiraishi and I
will stick close to Asirpa.
We'll get her to
Nopperabo's cell.
The lights are off
in the prison.
We'll move fast through
the dark and get close.
Toni Anji will take the lead.
The sound of the wind
is strong tonight,
but I can tell where I am
in relation to the buildings.
And it'll also help hide
the sound of my clicking.
[SUGIMOTO]
Okay, let's go.
♪
Who are you guys?
[groaning]
[muffled groaning]
I can't believe
they've already found us.
Toni, what the hell?
Do you have gunk in your ears?
[SUGIMOTO] How did you
miss them, you moron?
Hey, you're the idiots
who didn't realize
they had a damn lamp.
[ASIRPA]
Shh!
We've got this, get outta here.
Well, one thing is for sure.
Kadokura is now unemployed
and wanted.
Yeah, we're off to a bad start.
♪
[TONI]
This is it.
[NARRATOR] The Five Radial Wards
of the Abashiri Prison.
Capable of holding
over 700 prisoners.
And at the center
of the five wings
stands a central watchtower.
From that vantage point,
one can see the entire area.
[SHIRAISHI] If you look around,
you'll notice
that all the windows have bars.
Every single window
except one, that is.
The one on the ceiling.
That's our way in.
We just need to get up
to the roof.
♪
Hmm.
[grunts softly]
[saw whirring]
I can hear you, you know.
-[wood creaking]
-[gasps]
-Huh?
-[door opens]
[KADOKURA]
Oh, man.
It sure is windy out tonight.
-Yeah.
-[KADOKURA] Whoa!
Oh, no, look at that.
I broke my cup. Ow!
[SOLDIER 1]
Are you okay?
[SOLDIER 2]
Did you cut yourself?
[SOLDIER 1]
Don't worry, Chief Kadokura.
We'll get it cleaned up.
[KADOKURA]
Thanks.
♪
[lock clicking]
[lock opens]
[scoffs]
[gasps]
[ASIRPA]
Aca.
[WILK]
Asirpa, come here.
Ushiyama, where'd Hijikata
run off to?
Huh? He's not here?
[KIRORANKE] There's something
not right about that old man.
♪
[ASIRPA]
Aca?
Um, Aca?
Is it you?
It's me.
Asirpa.
I've come to see you.
Shiraishi, a match.
[MAN groaning]
[gasps]
[screaming]
[screaming continues]
That's not... my aca.
Intruders inside!
Kadokura!
Sugimoto!
Asirpa!
You run. You hear me?
Sugimoto!
[gunshot]
Uh... Why is my gun not working?
Mine isn't either.
You must not have cleaned 'em.
[screaming]
[SHIRAISHI] Do you think
this guy might be
Kiroranke's buddy?
The one Inkarmat
was talking about?
[SOLDIER] Enemy attack!
Get the hell up!
[clamoring]
[SUGIMOTO] Tell me,
are you with Kiroranke?
Answer me!
[groaning]
Looks like he's nothing
but a double, then.
Seriously, who would
go that far?
[SUGIMOTO]
Honestly? I don't know,
but somebody's gone through
some trouble to set us up.
[KADOKURA] You guys need
to stay right here.
Toni, stop.
We have to wait for Sugimoto!
Where are we going?
The tunnel is back
the other way.
I'll take you to the real one.
[ASIRPA]
Hmm?
♪
[bell ringing]
[SOLDIER]
Warden Inudou!
We've got intruders
in Ward Four!
So, they've finally come
for Nopperabo, then, have they?
[ringing continues]
This cannot be good.
Get back here, now.
Hmm?
[TANIGAKI] Inkarmat,
what are you doing here?
Tanigaki Nispa,
I'm asking you to run.
If you stay, you'll get
caught up in it, too.
[gasps]
There!
There they are!
[INKARMAT]
I used a false name.
Told them you'd send a telegram.
He knew when we'd
reach Abashiri.
Inkarmat, what do you mean?
Warden, there are lights
coming up the Abashiri River.
Awaiting your orders, sir.
[SOLDIER]
They're almost to the bridge.
[SOLDIER] Just take a breath
and remember all your training.
[INKARMAT gasps]
[TANIGAKI]
The bridge.
Looks like they're
actually doing it.
Lieutenant Tsurumi
and the Seventh Division?
Never underestimate
an intelligence officer's skill.
Tsurumi.
Has he been watching us
this entire time?
That's the only bridge
to the opposite shore.
Its destruction
will buy us some time.
Everyone,
get ready to fight, now!
[HAJIME]
The bridge is down, sir.
[TSURUMI]
Yes.
This is what
I've been waiting for.
[snickers]
♪
[NARRATOR]
Rear Admiral Heiji Koito,
commander of the Ominato
Guard District.
Second Lieutenant
Koito's father.
Go.
[SOLDIER] We've passed
the remains of the bridge!
This could get ugly.
We would take fewer casualties
if we let the orcas
battle each other
and became like
the disgusting creatures
that feed upon
their sinking carcasses.
No matter how well armed
they are,
they're still prison guards.
Tonight we'll prove that we're
on top of the food chain, men!
Our mission's simple,
capture Nopperabo and Asirpa!
[NARRATOR]
Next time, "Overwhelmed."