♪
[bell ringing]
[PRISONER 1]
We're under attack!
[PRISONER 2]
It's the Seventh Division!
[PRISONER 3]
We're all gonna get killed!
Open the doors!
This is great.
What the hell do we do?
We run, Shiraishi.
How about you think of a way
to get us out, Escape King?
[grunting]
Hold it right there.
Afraid you're not
going anywhere just yet.
♪
[bell ringing]
[TANIGAKI]
Let me get this straight.
This whole time, you've been
with Lieutenant Tsurumi?
-Why?
-[ringing continues]
[INKARMAT]
You hear that?
Sugimoto's group has failed.
Know what that means?
Now Tsurumi's the only one
who can get
Nopperabo and Asirpa out.
The trap has been sprung.
I don't understand.
The Seventh would get
all that Ainu gold.
Now you're okay with that?
[INKARMAT]
Let's be honest with each other.
It doesn't matter to me
who gets that gold,
and I suspect it doesn't matter
much to you, either.
[TANIGAKI]
Women are terrifying creatures.
[INUDOU]
You know what to do.
Get to your positions
and remember your training.
Put the Maxim guns
on both sides of the gate.
Concentrate your fire
on the entrance
when they break through,
and be relentless.
We're about to rip
these guys apart.
This is gonna save us
a fortune on pig food.
♪
[gasps]
Into the tunnel.
Hurry!
♪
[SOLDIER]
Fire!
[screams]
-[explosion]
-[TONI groaning]
I thought you wanted
to see your father.
Hmm.
Damn, that can't be good.
Time to go.
That's the wall
facing the river.
They've outsmarted us!
♪
[HAJIME]
Excuse me, Lieutenant.
If I may ask, what do you intend
to tell Central Command
about this?
Locusts, I think.
Locusts?
[TSURUMI]
It's happened before.
In 1882, the Japanese army
used ship cannons
in an attempt
to disperse locusts.
Here's our story,
in order to successfully
disperse a swarm of locusts
moving up the eastern
coastline of Hokkaido,
we requested direct aid
from Rear Admiral Koito,
the Commander of
the Ominato Guard District.
Agreed.
[TSURUMI]
During our return to Shari,
a riot broke out
at Abashiri Prison.
We happened to arrive
just in time
to help put an end to it.
I guarantee you,
no one from the mainland
is going to drag themselves
all the way out
to the ends of the earth
to investigate
either story for themselves.
Never have and never will.
They're content
just to read reports
and accept what we say.
If even a single person from
the prison survives, though,
we're screwed.
The entire thing comes apart.
What makes you think
there'll be any survivors here?
♪
[snickers]
[SOLDIER]
That's the actual army!
We can't fight that.
I'm surrendering.
But I heard they'll kill you
regardless.
That's a lie.
Warden Inudou spread that around
because he wanted us to think
we had no choice but to fight.
-[gunshots]
-[BOTH gasp]
[BOTH gasp]
[gasps]
They're here!
♪
Please! Don't shoot!
I surrender!
[groans]
Get to the cells!
Hurry!
Remember, they've come here
to kill us all.
If you don't fight back,
then today will assuredly
be your last on this earth.
[TANIGAKI]
Inkarmat!
Where are you?
-[INKARMAT] Tanigaki Nispa.
-Huh?
I'm coming.
Are you all right?
-[rumbling]
-[gasps]
Please get out while you can.
I'm not letting you die here.
[grunting]
[screaming]
Move!
-[INKARMAT breathing heavily]
-[TANIGAKI grunts]
[gasps]
[grunting]
Ushiyama.
[grunts]
Go on, get yourselves out.
Now you, Ushiyama.
Just drop it and run.
[grunting]
You two kids had damn well
better be happy together.
[BOTH gasp]
No, please.
What are you doing?
[grunting]
[screams]
That was really heavy.
Damn, got my jacket all dirty.
♪
Star shells were used
in the Russo-Japanese war.
♪
Sergeant Tsukishima, do it.
Yes, sir.
What'd they just throw at us?
Charge, men,
I want 'em all dead!
[SOLDIERS yelling]
Shiraishi, what the hell?
There's a narrow space
underneath each cell.
It's what allows air in
and keeps it circulating.
[screaming]
Damn it, would you just shut up?
Keep your nasty mouth shut.
[screaming]
[BOTH screaming]
[ASIRPA] Did you know
that Nopperabo was a fake?
Wait, did Kadokura know, too?
After we managed to escape,
Warden Inudou secretly
removed the real Nopperabo
and switched him out
for a decoy.
The thing is,
Kadokura spent seven years
seeing Nopperabo
every single day.
He simply isn't stupid enough
to not have noticed
the difference.
Then he had to have known this
when he sent them in there.
It's time for you
to come with us, Asirpa.
Or you'll miss your chance.
♪
[grunts]
They're here.
What are you doing? Run!
[gunshot]
Where is Nopperabo?
[gasps]
[KADOKURA]
Usami?
♪
Hmm.
[chuckles]
My, it's Immortal Sugimoto.
[ASIRPA]
I need to save him.
I'm not leaving here
without Sugimoto.
If Nopperabo could
finally see his daughter,
we feel that he might
then tell us
where the gold is being hidden.
That is what we all want.
Why we came here.
You know Sugimoto.
He would want to see
our goal achieved
more than he would
care about himself.
Get back!
So we're clear.
I haven't gotten the location
of the gold from him, yet.
Where is my Aca now?
[TSURUMI]
As it happens,
I've got 63
of my best men with me.
Do you really think
you're going to be able
to make some valiant escape?
Well, we're about to find out.
All of you, throw down
your weapons, and then--
[gasps]
[TSURUMI]
Nikaidou!
[grunts]
Let me go!
I'm gonna kill him.
That was the whole deal!
Don't be an idiot!
What happens if you end up
hitting Nopperabo?
[gasps]
All of you, I want you
out of the building, now!
I'll blow his head off,
I swear I will!
You got that?
Huh?
[USAMI]
Chief Kadokura, it's you.
[gasps]
It's so great to see you again.
[panting]
Get that crazy mole
away from me!
-[gunshot]
-[groans]
My apologies, Chief Kadokura.
I actually aimed for your neck.
Hmm?
[KADOKURA]
New kid, I just realized,
I haven't explained how this
little guy works yet, have I?
Hmm?
Hmm.
♪
It's a device that unlocks
every cell at once.
First used in Kabato Prison.
[gasps]
[laughs]
You feeling ready to face down
700 deadly criminals
with cabin fever?
Huh?
♪
[PRISONERS yelling]
[gasps]
Bayonets!
[yelling]
I want you to exterminate
every last one.
[yelling]
[gunshots]
[grunts]
Here I come!
[gasps]
Come out, wherever you are.
That old bastard.
Hijikata must've
set this whole thing up.
If Toni Anji
was working with him,
he might be with Asirpa now.
Hijikata's using us.
Damn schemer.
He sent us into the cell block
with the fake Nopperabo
because he knew
the commotion would cause
Inudou to panic
and bolt for the place
where the real Nopperabo
was being kept.
It's clear now.
That was the plan
from the very beginning.
[SUGIMOTO]
So while Kadokura and the guards
kept us pinned down here,
he would bring Asirpa
to meet her father,
learn the location of the gold
and escape.
[inaudible]
And as a bonus, he's using this
to separate me and Asirpa.
He knows
I'll get in his way, eventually.
♪
[grunting]
Easy.
You just have to
dislocate both shoulders.
[SUGIMOTO]
Are you kidding?
Just great.
There's gotta be another way out
besides this.
I'll find something
I can use to break the wall.
[SUGIMOTO]
No. I'll get out on my own.
Go look for Asirpa.
Once you've got her, go wait
for me at the main gate.
You better take care of her,
you hear me?
There. It's the chapel,
just like I thought.
Inudou comes here
every day to practice,
so I already had
my suspicions about it.
But no matter how many times
Kadokura searched the place,
he couldn't find
any hidden rooms.
You're saying
Aca is here, right?
[HIJIKATA] All we have to do
is catch Inudou
when he tries
to move Nopperabo.
[groaning]
What's wrong?
[TONI]
Let's get into the building.
My eardrums hurt.
Hmm.
Where'd she go?
Huh?
[ASIRPA panting]
[HIJIKATA] So she's headed back
to Sugimoto, huh?
She vanished the second
she learned the truth
about where
Nopperabo really was.
I'll say this,
that little girl's a tough one.
-Do we bring her back?
-Not now.
Our priority has to be
intercepting Inudou.
I guess I'll have to
resort to using these
in order to make him believe.
[panting]
[gasps]
Quiet.
[SOLDIER]
Hurry! Come on.
[sighs]
[ASIRPA]
Shiraishi.
Oh, there you are.
Where's Sugimoto?
[SHIRAISHI] He's still trapped
beneath the floors of the cells.
The air duct was so small
that only I could get out.
Hang on, wait.
You can't go after him.
There are too many soldiers.
But...
Asirpa, will you trust me
to go save Sugimoto?
Yes, and once you do, you should
take him to the chapel.
According to Hijikata,
that's where Nopperabo is kept.
But we really
can't do that, either.
I'm sorry.
Sugimoto instructed me
to take you to the main gate.
No.
I have to meet Aca
and see if it's really him.
No, listen, you can't go back
to Hijikata, you hear me?
For your own good.
We think he's been trying to
separate you from Sugimoto.
[gasps]
It won't work.
Once I save Sugimoto,
I'll go to the chapel.
As for Nopperabo, we'll get him
to the main gate.
[ASIRPA]
Wait.
Give it to Sugimoto.
[PRISONERS yelling]
♪
[grunting]
How the hell do you dislocate
your shoulders, anyway?
-[KIRORANKE] Sugimoto.
-[SUGIMOTO] Kiroranke.
Are you kidding me?
There's no way out of that.
What you doin'?
Gonna jam
a few of these grenades,
between the wall and the dirt.
[gasps]
[screams]
[KIRORANKE]
Might wanna back up!
Wait, just a sec!
Huh?
Did he fart?
[coughing]
The chapel, huh?
Asirpa said you should
show this to Nopperabo.
[sighs]
Yes, it's Asirpa's makiri.
The one her father made.
Go wait at the main gate,
she's alone with Shiraishi.
I'll make sure
Nopperabo gets there.
Give her my promise,
that she'll see him very soon.
Will do.
♪
[grunts]
[grunting]
[gasps]
I think I keep hearing
something from below.
So there's a basement
after all, then.
♪
[grunts]
Get out.
I will gladly put out
both of Inudou's beady eyes.
[groans]
♪
Huh!
Hmm.
[grunts]
Looks like it's till
death do us part, old man.
[screaming]
[grunting]
[groans]
[grunts]
[grunting]
[SUGIMOTO]
What?
[groaning]
Yohei, Sugimoto will be
joining you soon!
[grunting]
Hey, look.
Somebody's on the ground.
It's Nikaidou.
Is he alive?
♪
All right, Nopperabo,
let's get you to Asirpa.
She's waiting for you.
[SHIRAISHI]
Hmm.
Wait. Someone's coming.
Oh, look who it is.
Good to see ya.
Where's Sugimoto?
I was able to break him
out of the prison,
but then he went
to the chapel alone.
He sends his promise
that you'll meet Nopperabo soon.
Hijikata and Inudou are
both there at the chapel, too.
Let's go.
Nope, sorry,
you're staying here.
But...
Where are you going?
Maybe I can see
what's going on from up here.
[groaning]
[gasps]
[SUGIMOTO]
Blue eyes.
[NARRATOR]
Next time, "Call Out."