[owl hooting]
[MAN]
Pekanpe, huh?
You've got a lot, there.
I grabbed them as we passed
through Lake Touro.
Uh, they look old.
"Pekanpe" means
"things which float
on the surface of the lake."
They're water chestnuts.
A staple for us during winter.
They're really thorny.
I've heard that ancient ninjas
used to throw these things
on the ground to help impede
an enemy's advance.
Did they really?
[hooting]
Kotan-kor Kamuy
has been very noisy lately.
-[SUGIMOTO] Hmm?
-[ASIRPA] It's a type of owl.
A kamuy that protects
the village.
It yells at the demons
that come down
from the tops of the mountains.
[MAN] We can't just rely
on the kamuy for everything.
If they come,
the village men will be ready
and willing to risk
their lives to fight.
Who's "they"?
There's a group of bandits
that have come
to live in this area.
They attack at night,
moving through the forest
without even torches
to light the way.
Thing is, the light would make
no difference to them,
because they're all blind.
One of our people got a look
at them during an attack.
Apparently, the man
who's leading them
has some strange tattoos.
[ALL gasp]
An escaped prisoner
from Abashiri, then.
I bet it's a certain guy who was
doing hard labor on Mount Iwo.
His name is Toni Anji.
[SHIRAISHI]
It was a commonly held belief
that nobody sent to Mount Iwo
ever came back.
"Iwo" means "sulfur."
It's a critical resource used
in gunpowder and other things.
Unfortunately, mining it
releases sulfuric acid gas
which damages the eyesight
of those forced to dig it up.
It only took six months
for the entire operation
to be shut down.
And in that time, 42 died,
and who knows
how many went blind.
I heard a rumor that it was
secretly restarted, though.
And that Warden Inudou
is lending out prisoners
for the hard labor.
Anyway, I bet the ones
who escaped
before they were killed
are these bandits in the woods.
During the last new moon,
the village closest to ours
was attacked.
These men are very careful.
They attack villages together
in large groups
and they always do it
on a new moon
when there's no light.
Who knows when they'll attack.
It'd be faster
to find their hideout
than wait through the moon.
There's a Japanese family
that runs an inn
and hot springs fairly close by.
Perhaps you could learn
something from them?
Hot springs?
That sounds amazing.
I would kill for a bath.
[clicking]
Whatcha doin'?
Is something wrong?
No.
Just heard a sound
I've never heard before.
Hmm.
Maybe I imagined it.
[hooting]
[OLD MAN]
I've had my hands
on lots of different bodies
in my time,
but I swear I've never seen
such soft muscle before.
My hands sink into it.
You're like a big cat.
Well, maybe a tiger.
What a wonderful gift
heaven has given you.
But these,
the deep wounds that you have
scattered all over your body,
tell me, how were you
able to survive?
[SUGIMOTO]
The Ainu have a custom.
During their funerals,
the deceased person's
possessions are damaged
or destroyed.
That removes their souls,
so their owner can use them
in the next world.
If you want to remove my soul,
you'd need a bigger wound
than any of these.
[ASIRPA]
Their souls only leave
because they've finished
their job in this world.
I think the reason your wounds
have never killed you,
is that you still haven't
finished the job
you were meant to do.
[SUGIMOTO] I asked the masseuse
about the area.
He said there used to be
more hot spring inns
around here a while back.
Once they shut down Mount Iwo,
most of them closed up shop,
but the old buildings
are still in the forest.
[SHIRAISHI] Perfect places
for bandits to hide then, huh?
Anybody else up
for some hunting at dawn?
[MALE VOICE]
Wow!
[ASIRPA]
Would you like any help?
That's very kind.
But I'm more fit to walk
at night than you.
[ASIRPA]
Really?
[OLD MAN]
Indeed.
The blind don't see
with our eyes,
but that doesn't mean
we don't see.
A little tip, keep an ear out
for the sound of clogs
in the night.
What do you mean?
There's a certain sound
the blind bandits
make in the forest at night.
Everyone believes
it's the sound of clogs.
But they've got it wrong.
[click echoing]
[OLD MAN] I'll never forget
the first time I heard it.
It's actually their tongues,
you see.
They make a clicking noise
and use the echoes to see.
And the noise?
What exactly does
the click sound like?
[click echoing]
What the hell is that?
[ASIRPA]
They've got us.
This whole time,
they've been tracking us.
♪
Who the hell are you?
More over here.
[groans]
[SHIRAISHI]
That guy's Toni Anji!
[clicks tongue]
[SUGIMOTO]
It's too dark for us
to even see,
let alone fight.
And our dicks are out?!
Sorry, did we catch you
at a bad time?
Is that Shiraishi's voice?
Did you get hired on as a miner?
[grunts]
We're not here to deal with you!
Just let us copy down
your tattoo
and we'll give you a share!
The way I see it,
you'd have shot by now
if you weren't willing
to make a deal.
Nah, I'm just trying
to not hit the kid.
Now's your chance to get him out
before I start shooting.
-[gasps]
-[RYU barking]
[snarling]
Hey, that was Ryu!
It's too noisy to make
anything out for sure.
Go on, get him out of here.
Come on, let's go hide
in the forest!
-[groans]
-[thuds]
♪
[BANDIT]
Got him.
[groaning]
[grunting]
It'll take a lot more than this
if you wanna kill me!
-[clicks tongue]
-[gasps]
A gunshot.
[TANIGAKI] Toni Anji seems to be
the only one with a gun.
Maybe so they won't
shoot each other?
[KIRORANKE] They even approached
us from the direction of the inn
in order to keep us from
running toward the light.
They're obviously masters
at using the dark
to their advantage.
Ogata was the only one
who was smart enough
to stash his gun
near the hot springs.
We'll never hear
the end of that.
Hmm? [sniffing]
♪
Huh? Sugimoto.
[BANDIT]
Put out the light.
♪
You're gonna get yourself shot!
One of these guys has a gun!
[gunshot]
[gasps]
[shouting]
[clicks tongue]
[OGATA]
Can't see a thing.
And only four shots left.
Better not waste 'em.
[gasps, yells]
[SUGIMOTO whispering]
Asirpa, it's me.
Hmm?
[ASIRPA]
All this blood, is it yours?
Are you badly hurt?
I'm fine.
If it wasn't so damn dark,
they would be no match for me.
If we survive till dawn,
we'll counterattack.
[TONI]
Hmm. I think I smell blood.
♪
[sniffing]
[clicking tongue]
[WILK]
Are you really leaving?
I'll miss you.
I know.
Goodbye, Wilk.
[WILK]
Inkarmat.
This was my mother's.
I know that girls grow up
and change in no time.
Soon, you'll be even
more beautiful.
But if you'll wear this,
I'll recognize you
when we meet again.
Isn't it important to you?
[WILK]
Yes, but so are you.
[INKARMAT]
Thank you.
But I already know
that I'm never going to
see your face again.
That's what my fortune-telling
said my fate would be.
[TANIGAKI]
Inkarmat.
Hmm?
Tanigaki Nispa.
Where is Cikapasi?
I told him to hide and stay put.
If he's careful, the bandits
shouldn't find him.
[INKARMAT]
Let's hope so.
[clicking tongue]
-[ALL gasp]
-[clicking continues]
Here they come.
I have an idea. Follow me.
Hey, let's go. Come on.
♪
[KIRORANKE]
I found this place today.
If we cross the lake and take
the long route back,
we should be able to make it
to the inn
without them finding us.
Climb on board.
What is it, something wrong?
I'm sorry.
I'm afraid I can't swim.
And I have
a terrible premonition.
Don't worry, I've handled boats
like this since I was a kid,
and I've gone fishing at night.
I know what I'm doing.
[clicking tongue]
Think about it,
if I really wanted you gone,
then wouldn't I just
leave you here to die?
Get your ass in the boat!
[shudders]
[TONI]
Little more to the left.
Throw another one.
[ALL gasp]
-They're judging distance!
-[screams]
Tanigaki Nispa!
♪
[INKARMAT]
Oh, I see.
It's my time.
You're sending me
to the next world, aren't you?
This is my fate.
To die without ever
seeing him again.
The fortunes spoke true.
♪
[panting]
[BOTH gasp]
[ALL panting]
Are you all right?
How badly were you hit?
[TANIGAKI]
I'll be fine.
The bullet went clean through.
[laughs]
[TANIGAKI]
Seriously? You're laughing?
Kind of.
I just had the strangest dream.
I was remembering it.
Hmm.
[moans]
[INKARMAT]
Now I know.
We can change our fate.
Sorry to interrupt your fun
but we should really go.
-[groans]
-Huh?
He can see us!
♪
Dawn is coming.
Hurry, keep moving!
We'll be totally exposed here.
[mumbles]
[RYU barking]
Ryu?
[grunting]
Now the tables have turned.
Sugimoto!
♪
[SUGIMOTO]
Ogata.
Toni Anji and his men
just went inside.
This is their hideout.
[SUGIMOTO] If we go back
to get our guns, they'll escape.
Let's head inside
and finish this right now.
I want you to stay outside,
you got it?
♪
[SUGIMOTO]
It's dark.
I'm gonna open the windows.
[grunts]
Are you kidding me?
They nailed
all the windows shut.
[ASIRPA]
Sugimoto!
♪
-[clicks tongue]
-Go, now!
[panting]
[ASIRPA]
Sugimoto?
Huh? Asirpa?
How'd you get in here?
Where's Ogata?
[SUGIMOTO whispering]
We split up.
[ASIRPA]
It's not safe to move.
-What do we do?
-[clicking tongue]
Where is it coming from?
I can't see anything.
But this is their home.
They can see us perfectly.
[clicking continues]
[groans sharply]
That's pekanpe.
[groaning]
[grunting]
[clicks tongue]
[groaning]
[grunting]
You deserve every single bit
of this and more!
You miners and Warden Inudou
must be made to suffer
the way we did!
We're gonna take back everything
you've gained
by stealing the prisoners'
lives and sight.
[grunting]
[SUGIMOTO] Take this,
you goddamned bastard!
Where are you, Sugimoto?
Are you okay?
Asirpa, stay where you are!
Don't move!
Look at me.
You attacked
innocent Ainu villages.
Justice isn't on your side.
You're thieves!
Yes, you're right.
But it's the only way
for us to survive.
Now that we're
starving and blind.
We never killed anybody
who was innocent.
Whether that's true or not,
you're eventually going to.
[TONI]
You can tell, huh?
Even I can see it, you know.
No matter what, you can never go
back to who you were before,
isn't that right?
♪
[BOTH grunting]
[HIJIKATA] It's been
a long time, Toni Anji.
That voice.
What the hell are you
doing here, you old man?
Oh, not much,
just fighting Warden Inudou.
Hmm. Well, well.
We meet again, miss.
[ASIRPA]
Dick-sensei.
How were you able to find us?
[HIJIKATA]
The dog outside helped us.
We had information
that Toni Anji
was lurking around in this area.
Sugimoto, would you be willing
to leave Toni for us
to deal with in our own way?
As long as you let me
copy his tattoos, I don't care.
Although, Asirpa's relatives
do live right around here.
Probably better
to be safe than sorry.
Just go ahead and kill him
and skin him.
[ASIRPA] You live
in the darkness, always hiding.
Coming out only at night,
simply to harm others.
If you continue to do this,
your life will never
be anything but darkness.
[gasps]
Damn it, I know you're right.
♪
That's what
the warden's doing.
Lending out prisoners to work
Mount Iwo,
and then using
all that money to buy weapons.
I saw he even
had a Maxim gun.
If I had to guess,
I'd say it's likely
that he's hiding
other powerful weapons again.
[TSURUMI] But they caught you
before you were able to discover
where those weapons
were being held, so...
that's quite
a disappointing turn,
wouldn't you agree,
Private Usami?
[gasps]
[TSURUMI]
Tsukishima, sit him down.
Do you have any inkling
or even spark of an idea
how difficult it was
to get you hired on
as a guard there, to begin with?
Do you care to wager a guess?
[USAMI]
He's touching me!
[TSURUMI] I'm going to draw
a little stick figure
on this mole and make it run.
How about that?
Won't that be cute?
Ha! It's running
on his dumb face!
[TSURUMI] I'll make
the other mole run, too.
Why not, right?
[USAMI]
My head is going to explode.
[laughing]
[heavy breathing]
[TSURUMI] Aw, look,
those two moles are running
just as fast as they can.
But tragically there's no way
they'll ever get any closer,
no matter how hard they try.
Those poor things!
So, both Inkarmat and Kiroranke.
I wish that I could just
write it all off
as a trap of
Lieutenant Tsurumi's.
I've called an old friend
of mine to the city.
I've had suspicions of my own
and I'm ready
to find some answers.
I'll take photos of both of them
and have someone
look into it for us.
Why are we taking photos
all of a sudden?
[SUGIMOTO] I wanted to send
a picture of Asirpa
back to Huci.
But since we're here,
I figured we should
all take one.
Hijikata, I think I should
finally give you
what I've been keeping
safe here for so long.
♪
[HIJIKATA]
Ha. Hmm.
[TONI]
Sugimoto is his name, you said?
The strange thing is,
I felt something familiar
when fighting him.
I was struck by it.
He reminded me
of a young Hijikata,
back when I first
met him in Abashiri.
Fierce as a demon.
But somehow kind, as well.
[TANIGAKI]
Um, do I really have to strip?
[OLD MAN]
Everybody else did.
Looking good.
Spread your legs a little bit
more for me, though.
[camera shutter clicks]
♪
[NARRATOR] Next time,
"On the Night of the New Moon."