♪
[ASIRPA] Huki leaves
are a spring plant
and they can be eaten raw.
Ainu children snack on them
a lot when they're out playing.
But, look, they can turn
the area around your lips black,
so people can always tell
what you've been eating.
To the Ainu, there are
really only two seasons,
winter and summer.
Winter is when the men
go hunt in the mountains.
And when the ice
finally melts,
matnepa, the women's
season comes.
This is when they pick
lots of herbs
and vegetables to preserve.
That's the way to survive.
You work hard
and prepare during summer,
so you won't have to worry
about starving
in the long winter to come.
So women in every kotan
are about to be very busy.
♪
[birds chirping]
[MOTHER]
Oh, sounds like somebody's here.
Stay here. I'll get it.
Who would come by this early?
Coming.
Morning, sir, can I help you?
Please forgive my intrusion.
I don't mean to disturb you,
but is it true what I've heard,
that you're a taxidermist?
Yeah, that's right.
Uh...
Please, won't you come inside?
I'd be happy to show you.
[TSURUMI]
Thank you.
[door closes]
You see, I've been hoping
I could find a few mounts
to put up in the
Seventh Division's guesthouse.
I'll be damned,
you're as good as they said.
With so many lovely pieces,
how's a girl to choose?
My God, a polar bear.
Built that frame myself.
Sometimes I import
the pelts and cover models.
Curious, is this piece
still being worked on?
Is that why it's hanging
upside down?
[EDOGAI]
Yes, sir.
If you hang them like that,
the feathers fluff up
and look more realistic.
The goal is always
to make the animal appear
as if they're alive.
That's the true test
of a taxidermist's skill.
[TSURUMI]
I hope you don't mind me asking,
but is there sufficient demand
for taxidermists
in Yuubari to sustain
your business?
-[meows]
-Hmm!
It's a kitty! I love cats!
[EDOGAI] No. Most of my business
actually comes from overseas.
Wealthy people
all over the world
want taxidermies
of animals only found in Japan.
I was originally
born and raised in Nara,
but I moved to Hokkaido
to improve my craft.
The low temperature and dry air
are more conducive
to this kind of work.
And do you live alone here?
No, with my mother.
I'm afraid she has
a bad hip, though,
or she'd come out to greet you.
Oh, no.
I won't hear of it.
[sniffs]
Interesting.
So, the key to creating
a good mount
is fresh materials, right?
In other words, you need
an abundance of fresh corpses.
You strike me as a man
who really cares about his work.
You take pride,
a true craftsman.
Oh, I don't know.
I guess so.
Something wrong, Edogai?
-[shudders]
-I came to give your glove back.
I bet you're happy to see it.
[EDOGAI shuddering]
[MOTHER]
Huh, what could that noise be?
[MAN] Something seems
a little off to me.
[MOTHER]
Yasaku, did you hurt yourself?
Are you all right?
Yeah, it's nothing, okay?
I just dropped a mount,
that's all.
Look, I've never seen
that glove before.
Sorry, but it's not mine.
I understand.
You're surprised.
You thought you escaped us
last night.
We pretended we'd lost you,
then we followed you back.
And now, here we are.
[shuddering]
[KOUHEI] I don't know,
do you think he's got it?
[HAJIME] There was a rumor
several months ago
about a coal miner
with a strange tattoo
who'd died in an accident.
We eventually dug up
the grave, but it was empty.
Which means, the body
had to have been stolen
by a grave robber.
Drifters often work as miners,
and they don't survive long.
Like you mentioned,
the air is cool and dry,
so bodies don't rot
when they're buried.
Which means that Yuubari
is an excellent source
of fresh corpses.
Look, I don't know
what you're talking about, okay?
It's time for you to go!
Night after night,
you've been digging up
fresh bodies from the graveyard.
You stripped off their skin
in order to make this glove,
didn't you?
[heavy breathing]
It's fabulous!
And if I could, I'd like to put
in an order for one right now.
You would?
Even after heavy use,
it's still soft and comfortable
against the skin.
And it fits perfectly, so you
can even pick up tiny coins.
I've certainly
never seen its equal
with a normal
leather glove before.
So, you didn't come
to arrest me?
Lucky for you,
catching grave robbers
isn't one of my official duties.
-[sighs in relief]
-Hmm?
Sorry.
You see, it's just, that glove
isn't made of human skin at all.
It's only pigskin.
Pigs, huh?
Yeah, that's right,
and I used the hooves
to make the nails
and then glued them on.
To tell you the truth,
I'd gone to the graveyard
because I needed to get rid
of a whole bunch of
waste products from my work.
So for a minute,
I thought you'd found me out.
What a relief.
And, hey, uh,
if you like it that much,
then I want you to have it.
I have more in the back.
I'll go get one.
[MAN 1] You seem to be
enjoying yourself.
You're right. I really am.
[MAN 2] But you've only
just met this man, haven't you?
It's not very wise
to trust him so quickly.
[MAN 3]
I completely disagree!
Yasaku is a great judge
of character.
[MAN 4] Still,
it's better to be cautious.
[MAN 3]
That, right there,
that's why you have no friends.
[indistinct arguing]
Keep it down.
Guys, please be quiet.
Well, hello.
Greetings, everyone.
Tell me, are these all made
out of pigskin, too, Edogai?
[MOTHER] Kill him.
[MAN 1]
He's seen us. End him.
[MAN 2]
Stuff him and mount him.
-[MAN 1] Kill him.
-[MOTHER] Kill him.
[VOICES overlapping]
Kill him. Kill him.
Kill him. Kill him. Kill him.
Kill him.
[TSURUMI]
These truly look as though
they could come to life
at any moment.
You might be a genius, Edogai.
Huh?
[MOTHER]
Don't trust him, Yasaku.
Listen to me, he's a bad man!
[EDOGAI]
But, Mom, he likes my work.
How fascinating,
and are you the only one
who can hear her voice?
[MOTHER]
Kill him. He's seen us.
He can't leave alive.
[EDOGAI]
That's what you always say!
You try to drive everybody
away from me!
You killed Dad,
and he was my friend!
You know, son,
I'm afraid it's not healthy
to spend all day
talking to corpses.
[MOTHER]
Shut up, you stupid boy!
Your father was evil,
just like every other man!
Nobody loves you! Nobody!
[EDOGAI screaming]
Leave me alone!
[MOTHER]
That's why I castrated you.
You looked like him down there!
Edogai, I want you to listen
to my voice alone.
[MOTHER]
It was all for you!
[EDOGAI]
Stop it! Please!
[MOTHER]
I did it all for you!
Look at me, Edogai!
[EDOGAI]
Incredible.
That's human skin.
-Am I right?
-Yes.
What do you think of it?
I made it from skin
that I'd ripped off
the corpses myself.
[MOTHER] Don't you open your
heart up to him, you dumb boy!
Would you shut
the hell up, Mother?!
Shall we talk in your workshop?
[EDOGAI]
Oh-oh-oh.
You may not have done
the "sen" process
correctly during tanning.
"Sen"?
The process of scraping off
all the meat and fat
that are still stuck
to the skin.
If you're not careful,
the work won't last.
Your skin's a little rough here.
Did you happen to use alum
when you tanned it?
Yes.
That's not really the best
for people with sensitive skin.
I highly recommend
tannic acid instead.
It's plant-based,
so it's less abrasive.
[TSURUMI]
I wonder,
do you have any more
of your work,
and if so, would you
try it on for me?
[EDOGAI gasps]
You really mean it?
[meows]
Here's the first one.
What do you think?
It's so original!
This is truly
extraordinary work!
Whoa-oa-oa.
[TSURUMI]
I love it!
That's cutting-edge fashion,
is what that is.
Please show me more.
Show me more
of your beautiful creations,
dear Edogai!
A kitty!
Come on,
walk like a kitty for me.
That is so unbelievably cute!
♪
[sighs]
What the hell is going on?
Where is he?
[KOUHEI]
Hmm. No dice.
It's gotta be
Lieutenant Tsurumi's.
Oops.
Youhei's ear.
Oh, wait. Uh-oh.
So much fun!
Mother.
[MOTHER]
No!
[KOUHEI]
Found the ear.
Hey, what are you doing
to Mother?!
Listen. I want you to take this.
Time to let go
of those apron strings.
[gasps]
[MOTHER]
What kind of terrible son
points a gun at his own mother?
You decide.
Of your own free will.
-I can't.
-[MOTHER] No. Don't shoot!
You've gotta leave the nest.
Your nest was
a twisted place, son.
That's why you grew up twisted!
[MOTHER]
Don't do it!
[EDOGAI]
The voice, it's gone.
My mother passed away
due to a heart attack.
I should've ended things
while she was alive, though.
Thank you for making me do it.
By the way, son,
I was hoping
that we could make a deal.
What kinda deal?
The tattooed skins that
you and I are wearing right now
are actually only part
of a much larger code.
What I want is to make
false skins that look like these
but have wrong markings on them.
I want you to make
several clever fakes
which only you and I
can identify.
I believe that you and I
are going to work well together.
We'll create true chaos,
and what's better than that?
[USHIYAMA] How many tattoos
do we have so far?
Let's see here.
There's mine, obviously.
As well as Ienaga's.
One from you,
and the two that've been copied
onto oiled paper.
Plus the one that Private Ogata
acquired in Barato.
That makes six altogether.
So, the plan's to get
a bunch of crazies,
old men, and thugs together
to restore the Ezo Republic?
If this is just
some petty dream of revenge,
that's not very fair
to the people
who are following you, you know.
About Nopperabo,
he's an Ainu, right?
Do you think Lieutenant Tsurumi
actually knew that?
[OGATA] There was one
striking thing in common
about the belongings
of all seven men
that Nopperabo killed.
They were all damaged.
Ainu funerals involve damaging
the personal items of the dead,
which are then buried along
with that person for all time.
Ending their role in this world
for use in the next.
He ripped the bodies apart,
but he also took the time
to damage every single thing
that each of them owned.
In a way,
it feels like atonement.
The seven who were murdered
were from villages
all over Hokkaido.
They were going to use the gold
to buy weapons
to fight the Japanese.
If Nopperabo was trying
to help the Ainu
gain independence for Hokkaido,
then, why did he kill them?
Did he betray them
simply because he wanted
all the gold for himself?
But what if
he's not Ainu at all,
but actually a partisan
from the disputed territories
in Far Eastern Russia?
Russia is far cry from being
a unified place.
There are the forces
of the czar,
Lenin's Communist Party,
and then there are
the partisans,
composed of some
of the ethnic minorities.
Each one of these
different groups
are constantly fighting
the others.
So Nopperabo
was a partisan, then.
He tried to gather funds
for a war of independence
and he tried to move
the money out via Sakhalin,
but in the end, he failed.
And that's really how
this whole thing got started?
Think of that.
You never trusted Nopperabo
farther than you could
throw him, did you, old man?
I just realized,
this means No-Face's allies
outside the prison...
[HIJIKATA] Are very likely to be
partisans pretending to be Ainu.
[ASIRPA] The masu salmon
have come back again this year.
Aha! I can tell somebody's
been eating huki.
Obviously, so have you.
And Asirpa, too.
[gasps]
Are you kidding me?
How?
Asirpa, you might need
to cut back.
[laughing]
[ASIRPA]
This is maso salmon ohau.
The most delicious food
you can eat in the spring.
[ALL]
All right, let's eat.
Hinna, hinna.
It's great!
Man, that pukusa
is just so sweet.
Every time
we successfully survive
the long winter
eating dried foods,
it's always so wonderful
when spring comes
and you can eat
all the fresh things again.
The huki's a little bitter,
yet somehow sweet.
Bitter and sweet,
the flavor of spring.
[laughter]
[slurping]
[KIRORANKE]
So good.
[ASIRPA breathing heavily]
[grunts]
♪
[ASIRPA]
Will you tell me about Mommy?
[ASIRPA'S FATHER]
Again?
She was a beautiful woman,
just like you, sweet girl.
We met in Otaru,
and she taught me so many things
I didn't know.
The words of the Ainu
who lived here,
and everything they believed.
My blood, and the blood
of your mother's people,
you're a mix of both.
So you'll be a new kind
of Ainu woman.
One day, you're going to be
the leader of the Ainu.
Your eyes,
they're the same as mine.
I want you never to forget
what I'm about to say.
Inkarmat, no, well, okay.
[ASIRPA gasps]
Shiraishi! Wake up!
[grunts]
How long are you gonna
keep sleeping, you pig?
We're leaving now.
Yuubari's a long way off.
Is it just me, or do you seem
a little upset this morning?
[SUGIMOTO] Maybe she got a whiff
of your morning breath.
[EDOGAI]
Ohh, it's no good.
It's impossible to get
the exact same color this way.
This won't fool anybody.
I mean, you can really only
get that color
off a living human being.
Damn it! I can't do this!
I just can't do it!
Keep at it, Edogai.
Keep that focus.
Okay, how's this,
I'll tattoo you and rip off
your skin, sound good?!
Where's Tsurumi?!
I need to see him right now!
Where'd he go, anyway?
Lieutenant Tsurumi
returned to Otaru.
Well, I'm only taking orders
from him, got it?
I want to see Tsurumi!
Bring him here!
[screaming]
[SHOPKEEPER] Your friend here
doesn't look Ainu.
Interesting outfit you've got.
That a uniform under the jacket?
I need bullets.
Ones for this Murata gun.
You know,
just a little while ago,
an Ainu woman was in here.
She asked if I knew of a village
where an Ainu girl
with blue eyes lived.
Didn't your niece
have eyes like that?
Or is my memory failing me?
[MAKANAKKURU]
What was she like?
[SHOPKEEPER]
Well, she was pretty.
I think she said she was
a fortune-teller.
You appear to be walking
a lot better today.
Yeah, I am.
It barely hurts at all now.
So, what's next?
Where do you go from here?
Hmm!
[sighs]
A kill for the road?
It'll make a nice present.
[laughs]
He's stealing that winter coat
to take back to his nest.
This is perfect.
The deer hasn't noticed us yet.
[gasps]
Oh, hell, yeah!
[laughing]
I was actually planning
to aim for the neck.
Well, we got interrupted.
Nice job getting it in one shot.
[TANIGAKI]
Is that a boy from the village?
I've never seen him.
He's a little weird.
He never plays
with the other village kids,
but he always seems to be
plenty interested in the hunt.
[MAN]
Look at that!
Tanigaki's kid
put on a straw coat
and followed the hunt again.
If you want to watch
from close up,
gather some pine boughs for us.
[gasps]
The front legs of a yuk
are only connected by muscle,
so they're easy to detach.
Ah!
That's yours.
You're serious?
[MAKANAKKURU]
Oh.
I see you were born
an Ani Matagi.
You do it right.
I don't get it, though.
This yuk's too young
to be alone.
He must've just
left his parents,
or maybe they're dead.
I guess he's just like me.
He's alone, his family
is all dead.
The old folks in the village
take care of him.
And his real Ainu name...
Your parents gave it to you
before they died, right?
Cikapasi.
Great name, huh?
Yeah.
Cikapasi?
What does that mean?
[MAKANAKKURU]
"He who makes the birds fly,"
but it also means,
"to get an erection."
So, your name's "Hard-on"?
I agree
with your prior assessment.
-Cikapasi.
-Hmm.
It's a really great name.
"Hard-on."
-[villagers gasping, murmuring]
-[MAN speaking Ainu]
[MAN]
Ayapo.
[WOMAN]
Anpene.
[MAN continues speaking Ainu]
Oh, look.
What a wonderful Nispa
we have joining us.
I love a man with a scar
on his face, my favorite.
I'm Inkarmat, at your service.
It means "the woman who sees."
You there, the handsome Nispa.
Shall I tell your fortune?
No thanks. I'll pass.
Tell me, did you lose
your little sister?
[groans]
The thought just came to me
as I looked at you
standing there.
I'm very sorry.
[TANIGAKI]
Who are you?
I'm no one, but I'm here
in search of someone.
I wonder if you could
help me with that.
I'm looking for a girl
with blue eyes.
My Sirakki Kamuy says
this is the right place.
We met in Naganuma.
She said she was traveling
with a goal in mind.
She had three Nispa with her.
[speaking Ainu]
And one of them is going
to betray little Asirpa.
[continues speaking Ainu]
[INKARMAT]
He's a very dangerous man.
If he's not stopped,
her life may very well
be in grave danger.
[MAKANAKKURU speaking Ainu]
[TANIGAKI]
I'll bring Asirpa back safely.
I promise.
Osoma, your turn.
Isn't there something
you want to give him?
[sobbing]
[MAKANAKKURU]
She spent a long time
trying to make you tekunpe,
with Huci's help.
She only managed to get
one done in time, though.
When an Ainu woman's in love,
she makes a pair of tekunpe
to give her man.
Thank you, Osoma.
I promise I'll come back,
so you better make me
the other one.
Mm-hmm.
[speaking Ainu]
Shall I tell your fortune?
It could help you find Asirpa.
No, don't bother.
I'm not going because I believe
in your fortune-telling.
The problem is, you seem
to have the villagers convinced.
The Sirakki Kamuy tells me
that good fortune
lies to the east.
Let's be off, Tanigaki Nispa.
Wait. Why are you
coming with me?
I already told you.
I have a weakness for a man
with a scar on his face.
[TSURUMI]
Hmm. I see.
Use the man named Tanigaki
who's staying with the Ainu
at the kotan.
With any luck, I think his leg
should have healed by now.
[NARRATOR]
Next time: "Fakes"