♪
Corpse in a uniform?
Nah, ain't seen that.
[KIRORANKE]
Do you think he's alive?
[NAGAKURA] I have no idea,
but we aren't leaving Yuubari
till we have a definitive answer
on Sergeant Tsukishima.
♪
[HIJIKATA]
There must be a clue here,
we just have to find it.
There's obviously
some connection
between the leftover skins
used for all this taxidermy
and the fake tattooed skins
that we're looking for.
[gasps]
Ahh.
Yep. They're thorough.
[panting]
[OGATA]
Don't go outside.
You'll get shot.
They're out there.
I caught a glimpse of a uniform.
More than one, I think.
It seems to me these bastards
are only here
to destroy the evidence
of the fake skins.
[KOUHEI] The problem is,
there may be kibushi berries
still left in Edogai's house.
Get it?
They are used to do
the tannin tanning,
which means, we've got
to get rid of them fast.
♪
[KOUHEI]
From the looks of it,
there are two or three people
inside the house.
If Tsukishima's report
is correct,
do not kill Saichi Sugimoto
on sight, do you hear me?
He's mine.
If Lieutenant Tsurumi's men
received an order to come here,
then I guess we should assume
Sergeant Tsukishima
did make it out
of those tunnels alive.
Yeah, there's no doubt.
The windows are all barred.
So, if those soldiers
wanna come inside,
they'll have no other choice
but to use the front door.
And I'm gonna make double sure
that's the case.
♪
Up high!
[gunshot]
Take cover under the awning!
We're going through.
-Come on.
-Ah!
Back up.
[grunts]
No, keep under the awning.
-[gunshot]
-[glass shatters]
♪
[OGATA]
Looks like quite a few of 'em.
Advance to the second floor.
We've got to take out
that sniper.
[gasps]
[grunting]
[gunshot]
-[rattling]
-Hmm.
♪
[grunts]
-[groans]
-[SOLDIER] Get the hell off!
[grunts]
[IENAGA coughing]
[IENAGA exhales]
I can't get out.
-[rattling]
-[gasps]
Ushiyama!
Gotta move, Ienaga.
♪
[rattling]
[grunting]
Die! Die!
You bastard!
[groans]
[body thuds]
What, are you waiting
for some kinda thank you
or something?
It's not like I saved you
because I wanted to,
just to be clear.
[grunting]
[SUGIMOTO]
Hijikata, where are you?
Hijikata!
[snickers]
There you are, Sugimoto!
[groans]
-[whimpers]
-Stay back. He will shoot.
One finger out of place
and you'll lose it.
Come on, it's our only chance,
hurry up.
Time to go, old man.
♪
Let's split up into two groups.
We'll meet at Ashibetsu.
My group will see
if we can track down Nagakura.
You know, with no real way
to tell which skins are fake,
we're gonna have to talk
with Nopperabo directly.
I bet he'd be willing to share
his secrets with his daughter.
So, you knew who she was.
I should've assumed you would.
For my part, as long
as I get a small share,
I don't really care who does
what with all that gold.
But Asirpa,
she's a true Ainu.
Could the person who stole
from her people
really be her own father?
I wanna see her
find the truth.
She deserves that.
Then is it safe to assume
we share the same goal,
at least for now?
Meaning, we'll both do
whatever we like.
♪
[screaming]
[meows]
[SUGIMOTO]
We should be careful.
Stay out of sight and avoid
people as much as possible.
It won't be long before they
start talking to the locals.
They'll track us that way.
Huh?
Look, Sugimoto.
Those are tureptacir.
Woodcock birds.
This is their time,
herb-gathering season.
That's when the woodcocks
always come home.
Why are they digging holes?
Are they looking for bugs?
[ASIRPA] Their long beaks,
which they use to find food,
are similar to the tools
the Ainu use
to dig up ubayuri roots.
So we call them
"ubayuri-digging birds."
Are they tasty?
Their brains are so good.
-[rifle cocks]
-[gasps]
Hey, Ogata, don't use that.
Why not?
We're eating them, aren't we?
Yeah, but if you
hit one with that,
the others will fly away.
Woodcocks don't fly
in a straight line,
so it'll be pretty hard
to hit one with that gun.
The Ainu have a trap
that takes advantage
of the woodcocks'
natural instincts.
You make a windy path
with branches
that they'll want to follow,
and you fill it up with traps.
That way, you catch enough
for everyone.
-Hmm.
-[chuckles]
[ASIRPA] See?
The traps worked!
Okay, but that's still probably
not enough for everyb--
[grunting]
Just make yourself useful
and help me pluck feathers.
I think she's
a little bit disappointed.
She set all those traps
and only caught two.
Hmm?
Three, huh?
I wondered
where you went off to.
I'm impressed you managed to get
so many without buckshot.
Hmm.
[USHIYAMA]
Man, you are annoying, though.
So Asirpa says he can't do it,
and he works himself up
into a huff. Ugh.
You know you're
really just jealous
because you can't
hit shit with a gun.
Am not.
[ASIRPA] Dick-sensei,
this is woodcock brain.
Mm. Mm!
Say it isn't so.
Could it be,
you don't like brains?
Mm. Mm. Mm.
Don't mess with me.
Is that even edible?
[ASIRPA]
Sugimoto, it's hinna, right?
Oh, yeah. Hinna, hinna.
Aw!
Hmm. Hmm!
[gulps]
[groaning]
Ahh!
Nope. I'm fine.
[grunting]
[gasping]
[ASIRPA] Now we'll use
the rest to make chitatap.
Hell, yes!
-Chitatap time!
-What's that?
You chop the meat up
while saying "chitatap."
Wanna try it?
[USHIYAMA]
Chitatap.
Chitatap. Chitatap.
-Chitatap. Chitatap.
-Take over for him, Ogata.
Chitatap.
Everybody has to help
with chitatap.
[USHIYAMA]
Chitatap.
♪
Asirpa.
Ogata isn't saying "chitatap."
[ASIRPA]
Hmm.
[exhales sharply]
Ogata?
Is there a problem?
The finished product:
ohau made from
woodcock chitatap.
So ready for this.
Oh, oh, oh.
Delicious!
Hinna, hinna.
-[USHIYAMA] Yum!
-Mmm!
[SUGIMOTO]
Oh, so hinna!
[MAN]
Hey, you there.
Why pretend to be Ainu?
You're Japanese, aren't you?
Hmm?
[MAN] An Ainu child traveling
with three men, huh?
I haven't seen anything
like that.
Wait, is that the kid
you're talking about?
-Hmm?
-[CIKAPASI grunts]
-[groaning]
-[door opens]
Hard-on, don't run off.
Stop calling me that.
It's not my name.
My real name is Cikapasi.
You know, it's pretty obvious
you've been following us.
I just assumed
that eventually you'd give up.
You should go back.
Your people must be worried.
They're not. My family's dead.
Nobody's waiting for me at home.
Why can't I come with you?
[INKARMAT]
It's not a bad idea.
-Hmm?
-Huh?
[INKARMAT]
The Sirakki Kamuy says
it's actually very good luck
to bring him along with us.
And if we pretend
to be a family,
it'll eliminate suspicion.
Really?
We're pretending to be a family?
Wait. That means
Inkarmat'll be my big sister.
With different mothers,
obviously.
So, our story is, you love
your little brother
and you let him grab your boobs.
And we're on a journey together,
searching for our dad,
who we've never met.
[chuckles]
Yeah, I like that.
Sounds like fun.
[CIKAPASI] And you're
my dad's little brother,
Tanigaki Nispa.
You've been traveling with us
and Inkarmat likes you
in a certain way,
but you're hiding the fact
that you're really her brother.
That's too complicated.
Also, it's disturbing.
[CIKAPASI]
It is?
Okay, so,
Inkarmat is my big sister,
and she definitely doesn't
get mad if I grab her boobs.
And you're the guy
who lives next door
and you have these
super giant testicles.
I think you've
missed the point.
I've been wondering, do you know
if he is still in Abishiri?
[HIJIKATA]
Yes.
Who is this "he"?
Shirosuke Inudou.
He's the warden
of Abashiri Prison.
He and I happened to have
a rather memorable history
at Kabato Prison, as well.
Speaking of Kabato,
I'll never forget the day
you nearly shocked me to death.
Thank you, sensei.
Travel safe, and we'll see you
when you return.
Indeed. Have a nice year.
♪
Gamushin.
[gasps]
That's impossible.
Hijikata, is that really you?
Inudou, you're truly despicable.
I've been a swordsmanship
instructor at this institution
for the past
two decades of my life.
Why did you never tell me?
From what I understood,
you two parted ways
back before
the Hakodate War, right?
I'm under no obligation
to give prisoner information
to unrelated persons.
You lost your brother
in the Hakodate War
when he fought
on the new government's side.
You may hate him
because of that,
but why hide him
from the government?
Why keep him hidden
instead of executing him?
Perhaps you decided
that the worst punishment
for a man like
Toshizou Hijikata,
was to steal everything
he cared about
and force him to live a life
empty of meaning.
I've been waiting
for his light to go out.
Hmm?
When the light
finally leaves his eyes,
I'll hang him.
Let me see him.
I think you need to leave.
I know you're being
transferred to Abashiri
at the start of the year.
So I'll just come back then.
[INDOU] Hijikata will be moved
to Abashiri, as well.
You're a monster of a warden,
you know?
An obsession with rules is fine,
but you're obsessed
with revenge.
[door opens, closes]
♪
[door opens]
If you don't let me
see him right now,
I'll split your head open!
-No! Sir, please!
-[grunting]
[INDOU] Get that old geezer
the hell out of here.
Drag him out the gates
if you have to.
[grunting]
Let me go, damn bureaucrats!
-Calm yourself, sensei.
-Huh?
[SOLDIER]
Come with me, sir.
[CHIEF GUARD]
He's in solitary over there.
Ten minutes,
that's all I can swing, okay?
I really owe you one.
-Thank you, chief.
-It's nothing.
See, I'm a swordsman,
so I understand.
Hmm.
[HIJIKATA]
That you, Gamushin?
[gasps]
I never thought I would
hear that name again at my age.
It was the fourth year
of the Keiou era
when last we met, wasn't it?
[NAGAKURA]
Yes, that's right.
I gave up on the Shinsengumi
at that point.
But, Hijikata,
even if I had my disagreements
with Kondou,
everything I did
for Shinsengumi,
I did because of you.
What the hell's
gotten into you, Shinpachi?
Has old age finally
softened you up a bit?
[NAGAKURA] Brother, if you
hadn't protected me from Kondou,
I would've been forced
to commit seppuku so many times.
[HIJIKATA] You liked the ladies
a little too much,
as I remember.
[NAGAKURA]
What are you trying to say?
You're the one who taught me
that bad habit.
[HIJIKATA] We both did
a lot of stupid things.
We loved swords,
wandering, and women
more than anything else.
We were an awful lot alike.
[NAGAKURA]
Remember your nickname?
I can't believe I'm thinking
of that right now,
but it was Baragaki,
"a kid as violent as a thorn."
What a stupid name.
[HIJIKATA] Oh? It's a damn sight
better than "Gamushin"
or "Reckless Shinpachi."
You were dumb
and a pain in the ass,
but when you swung your sword,
it was a thing of beauty.
And beautiful things
should live.
So you said.
When we had
that last horrible fight
before we parted ways,
was that actually
you trying to keep me
from following you
to your death?
I've spent countless nights
lying awake asking myself that.
Wondering if that was
the last thing
all of you did for me
to keep me safe.
Am I wrong, Hijikata?!
You are.
I just didn't like you
because you were an idiot.
[sobbing quietly]
[SUGIMOTO]
Hey, Asirpa.
Are you sure we haven't seen
Hijikata somewhere?
I feel positive
I've seen that face before.
Hmm?
[snoring]
[rustling]
[SUGIMOTO]
Oh, it's just an Ogata.
[KIRORANKE] There are
fake tattoos out there.
Going to Yuubari gave us
this valuable information.
That was a big miscalculation
on Lieutenant Tsurumi's part.
He probably didn't expect us
to find out quite so soon.
[HAJIME]
I'm sorry, lieutenant.
I'm afraid they escaped.
It's fine.
At the end of the day,
it really doesn't matter
whether or not they know
the fakes exist.
I only wanted one thing,
and I got it.
Chaos.
As long as we can keep gathering
the real skins one by one,
that's all we actually need.
Won't it be fun to watch them
run around helplessly,
uncertain of what's real
and what's not, Tsukishima?
Yes, sir.
[snickers]
Without any surefire way to tell
which ones are the fakes,
gathering the skins
will not be enough
to help us crack that code.
There may be no obvious way
to tell the difference at all.
[NAGAKURA] Well, that would be
quite a disappointment,
wouldn't it?
I suppose we'll have to try
to rely on this man.
Uh, who, me?
Never would've thought
that this useless idiot
would one day
be our last hope.
The fastest way forward
is to talk to Nopperabo
in Abashiri Prison directly.
It's up to you to get us in,
Escape King,
Pee break!
[footsteps approaching]
[SUGIMOTO]
Shiraishi.
Huh?
[SHIRAISHI laughing]
Good to see you, Sugimoto.
How were you able to find us?
Forget that.
We need to talk.
-Come with me.
-Uh...
[SHIRAISHI]
Where's everybody else?
[SUGIMOTO]
I remembered something.
[SHIRAISHI]
Oh, yeah?
[SUGIMOTO]
After Kazuo Henmi died,
we met a weird guy
at the longhouse, remember?
It was Toshizou Hijikata.
I'm sure of it.
[gasps]
[SUGIMOTO] So, I guess,
you were working with him then?
You were passing him
information about us
the whole time, weren't you?
[gasps]
No.
Man, I was super drunk
at the longhouse.
[SUGIMOTO] Are you really
still gonna lie to me?
If you'd told the truth,
I would've forgiven you.
-[screaming]
-[yelling]
[screaming]
[grunting]
Don't!
[heavy breathing]
-[snoring]
-Huh?
[sighs]
[SHIRAISHI]
Oh, jeez. What do I do?
Now I'm scared shitless.
The gold won't matter
if he kills me first.
[grunts]
[barking]
[sighs]
[grunts]
Hey.
You're Shiraishi, aren't you?
[chuckles nervously]
[NARRATOR]
Next time,
"The Great Plan
to Infiltrate the Asahikawa
Seventh Division."