[SHIRAISHI]
A sunfish?
[SUGIMOTO] During the summer,
sunfish float up
to the surface to take a nap.
So it's easy to climb on top
of 'em and harvest the meat.
Jeez. You'll really do anything
to eat in-season fish.
[INKARMAT] Here. I sewed it
back up for you.
Thank you.
You've done so much for me.
Not to mention, Cikapasi.
[INKARMAT]
Not at all.
I feel a lot safer on the road
having a man along.
It's not that I haven't noticed
you're usually cold to me,
but you're always kind
when it counts.
Hmm.
[FISHERMAN speaking
in Satsuma dialect]
Huh?
He's offering us
that sea otter meat.
Sea otter?
I've never tried it.
Thank you.
[speaking in Satsuma dialect]
[gasps]
[TANIGAKI]
What'd he say?
Hmm.
You know what we need?
Beach rose fruit.
-Oh...
-Huh?
What is that?
Looks like a big, black cloud.
[growling]
[grunts]
Grasshopper.
I hate these things.
[grunts]
And you call yourself
"immortal."
Hey, guys, we got a problem.
-Huh?
-Hmm?
[ALL screaming]
[screaming]
[SUGIMOTO] They're trying
to bite through our clothes!
-[screaming]
-[TANIGAKI] That police lodge.
Let's take cover there!
Come on!
Inkarmat is still
out here somewhere!
[SUGIMOTO]
She'll be fine! Just get inside!
-[TANIGAKI grunts]
-[SUGIMOTO] Ow! Ow! Ow! Go!
[SHIRAISHI]
What the hell are those things?!
♪
[OGATA]
A locust swarm.
When the conditions are right,
like after a flood or something,
you get a ton
of these nasty things.
They move in huge swarms
and cover dozens of kilometers.
They can even cross the sea.
It's not just the crops
they eat.
They'll eat through paper walls
and even kimonos.
How long do you think it might
take for them to pass by?
I'm really hungry.
Where is Asirpa?
I hope she's okay.
[INKARMAT panting]
♪
[ASIRPA]
Inkarmat!
Here.
You really saved me.
We should be safe out
on the water.
I wanted to speak
with you alone, anyway.
Here's my chance.
I want you to tell me everything
you know about my father.
So sea otter meat
has kind of a unique smell,
wouldn't you say?
Are you sure it's even edible?
[sighs]
[SUGIMOTO]
What's going on?
Something's weird.
Why does Shiraishi look... sexy?
[TANIGAKI]
Sugimoto, you okay?
[gasps]
Oh, my.
I lost another button.
[SHIRAISHI]
That Matagi.
He's so dreamy.
Oh!
Ah, I feel dizzy. Weird.
Ogata, you okay?
[SUGIMOTO]
Lie down, immediately!
[groans]
Let's unbutton your shirt
so you can breathe better.
Pants, too!
I think it's important
he takes off everything!
[gasps]
[door opens, closes]
[KIRORANKE]
Ow, that hurt.
They nipped at my ears.
Hey, there, what you guys up to?
Kiroranke.
[ALL gasp]
The truth is, I knew
your father very well, Asirpa.
In fact, I was close to your age
now the first time I met him.
What about now, do you hate him?
Of course not.
I've always been on his side
and yours, don't you see?
You think I'm that stupid?
You used lies to scare Huci,
and then you used
Tanigaki to follow me.
[INKARMAT]
I never lied to Huci.
You should return to Otaru.
I don't believe
in fortune-telling.
I need to know the truth,
and I'm planning to find
it out for myself.
[INKARMAT] Nopperabo,
the man in Abashiri Prison,
he isn't your father, Asirpa.
[gasps]
[INKARMAT]
Your father's name was Wilk.
He was never a man who'd be
morally capable of killing Ainu
and stealing their gold.
I remember the day
I first met him.
Wilk had only
just arrived in Hokkaido,
and he spoke Ainu
with a Sakhalin accent.
He had deep, blue eyes,
just like yours.
[gasps]
He told me that he'd been born
to a Polish father
and a Sakhalin Ainu mother.
He explained that many of
the people living on Sakhalin
were Poles who had been
oppressed by the czar
and exiled to the Far East.
Wilk had worked with other
ethnic minorities
since he was young,
fighting alongside them for
their liberation from the czar.
He was wounded in that fight
and fled to Otaru in Hokkaido.
At the time, I'd already begun
traveling as a fortune-teller,
and we spent every day together.
Wilk listened to everything
I told him
about the Ainu and our ways.
Our beliefs, customs,
language, food, everything.
He recovered
from his wounds here.
And the more he learned
of the Hokkaido Ainu,
the more he came to love them.
♪
[ASIRPA] I don't believe
that my father is Nopperabo
any more than you do.
But still, my father never
once told me anything about you.
He always claimed
that he learned everything
about the Ainu
from my mother.
I don't think I can believe
anything you say.
[gasps]
I guess to Wilk I was still
just a child and not important.
Maybe he really forgot about me.
If you agree Nopperabo
is a different person,
then where is
my father right now?
He's gone.
My poor Wilk.
He was murdered.
[gasps]
By Kiroranke, a former friend.
♪
[KIRORANKE] I got separated from
Hijikata's group at Asahikawa,
and I haven't seen
any of them since.
I guessed that you'd most likely
head down
the mountains to Tokachi
in order to avoid
running into the Seventh.
Then, I heard a rumor
at a local kotan
that someone
had actually seen you.
Anyway, let's get back
to the present.
Sugimoto, is it just me,
or have you grown sexier
since the last time we met?
Come on, stop.
[SHIRAISHI]
So cute!
-[KIRORANKE] So cute.
-[TANIGAKI] So cute.
And you, Kiro,
you kinda look like you've been
working out, too,
am I right, huh?
Oh, do you really think so?
You agree, Tanigaki?
[groaning]
[TANIGAKI]
What's happening?
This feeling,
I can't control it.
[SHIRAISHI]
I've never felt this before.
What do I do?
Things are about to get weird
if it doesn't go away.
[exhales sharply]
♪
Yeah, that's it.
I can't control it anymore.
I have to be free!
-Let's play sumo!
-[ALL] Yes.
[ALL]
Great idea!
[grunting]
[groaning]
[laughing]
[ALL sighing]
♪
[ALL]
That was so hot.
[SHIRAISHI] Hey. Looks like
the grasshoppers are gone.
Yeah. Seems that way.
We got a little
outta control in there.
[ALL]
Yeah...
Tell no one of this.
-[chuckles]
-Hmm.
Inkarmat?
[INKARMAT] It's believed
that the meat of sea otters
acts as a powerful aphrodisiac.
Did you know,
when one loses a partner,
they have no outlet for
their lust, and so, they die.
Whoa, hey. Hold on.
What are you doing?
If it makes you feel better,
you can always just blame it
on the sea otter meat.
[moaning softly]
[gasps]
[BOTH moaning]
♪
[INKARMAT]
If you go to Abashiri,
you'll run into Kiroranke again.
He's a dangerous man.
In the end, you'll lose
both the gold and the tattoos.
I can't imagine Kiroranke Nispa
killing my father.
[INKARMAT]
I have proof.
-[INKARMAT] Asirpa.
-Huh?
Have you been here all night?
Hey. Look at that, guys.
Asirpa's doing just fine.
Thank goodness for that.
-Glad you're safe.
-[gasps]
[INKARMAT]
Kiroranke.
What is he doing here?
Hey, there. How have you been?
Huh?
Kiroranke Nispa.
Are you the one
who killed my father?
[gasps]
You're serious?
Come on, now, where is
this coming from?
[INKARMAT] She confronts him
directly right after I tell her?
That foolish girl.
-Here's the proof.
-[gasps]
The fingerprints
left on this betting ticket.
What?
Fingerprints?
Inkarmat.
Every set of fingerprints
is entirely unique unto itself.
They've been used for years
outside of Japan.
It's very helpful
in criminal investigations.
At the horse racing track
in Naganuma,
I took fingerprints
from all of the men,
and I had them matched.
To my surprise, Kiroranke's
ended up matching some
which were found
several years ago
in a rather shocking place.
The place where Asirpa's father
had been murdered.
-[gasps]
-What are you suggesting?
She said your prints were found
on his makiri blade.
You claimed you hadn't seen
my father for years, right?
This is nuts.
I mean, if I'm the killer,
then who's Nopperabo?
The guy that's in prison?
[OGATA]
Everyone, hold it.
-[rifle cocks]
-This is about her.
She's been working
with Lieutenant Tsurumi.
Stop this.
What proof do you have?
Oh, poor Genjirou Tanigaki.
She's got you wrapped around
her little finger, huh?
It was Lieutenant Tsurumi
who recovered the items
left at the murder scene.
In other words,
he's the only one
with the recorded fingerprints.
[gasps]
I was just using
Lieutenant Tsurumi.
[TANIGAKI gasps]
Gotta admit, she's a hell
of a woman, ain't she, Tanigaki?
How can you trust
any information from that man?
If we start killing each other,
we're giving him what he wants.
Hear me out.
Asirpa, I don't blame you
for not wanting to believe
your father is Nopperabo.
But there can't be
that many people in the world
capable of coming up
with the idea
of tattooing a code
on human skin.
Do you hear me?
I think you know that, right?
This is tense.
What do you think?
I mean, which one
is telling the truth?
♪
Shiraishi.
You're the only one who actually
met Nopperabo in jail.
Maybe you could help here.
[SUGIMOTO]
That's true.
Did he really have
blue eyes like Asirpa?
Uh... I don't know.
I never said anything about him
having blue eyes.
To be honest,
he isn't exactly the kinda guy
you wanna spend
a lot of time staring at.
[SUGIMOTO]
Nopperabo. The man with no face.
[SHIRAISHI] From what I know,
all he actually did
was make the tattoos.
As far as the escape plan goes,
old No Face wasn't
the one behind it.
The mastermind for that
was Hijikata.
[SUGIMOTO]
Makes you wonder.
Maybe Toshizou Hijikata
set the whole thing up.
[TANIGAKI] I don't know
what you want, Inkarmat.
I just want to protect the gold.
I'm an Ainu woman, after all.
What about
Asirpa's father, Wilk?
Did he feel the same way as you?
Yes.
That's why he was killed
by Kiroranke,
a fellow member
of his guerrilla organization.
That's what I think, anyway.
You know what I think?
Tsurumi might've falsified
those fingerprints.
Sure, it's possible.
But if I end up dead
sometime in the near future,
know it'll be Kiroranke
who kills me.
[TANIGAKI] Did you sleep with me
to protect yourself from him?
Tell me the truth.
'Course not.
What happened last night
was due to the sea otter.
[TANIGAKI]
Sea otter!
[HAJIME]
Another telegram arrived
for the old Ainu lady in Otaru
from Tanigaki in Kushiro.
It would appear that he's met up
with them, now.
[TSURUMI]
Good.
Then, I think
it's just about time
we head to Abashiri, too.
[KIRORANKE]
My sons are all Hokkaido Ainu.
So I believe the gold belongs
to the Ainu of this land.
My goal is exactly
the same as yours.
Okay, so what do we do now?
With everyone being suspicious
of each other.
That's a good point.
I'd really prefer not to get
murdered in my sleep.
♪
I say we keep moving.
Once we meet Nopperabo,
it'll all be clear.
Asirpa will know the truth.
Our goal hasn't changed at all.
We're going to Abashiri.
So, let's do it.
Inkarmat and Kiroranke?
A little warning.
If either of you end up dead
on this journey,
I promise you,
I have no problem
killing whoever's left.
I'm just kidding.
[laughing]
♪
[footsteps]
Huh?
-[KADOKURA] New kid!
-[gasps]
Are you still curious
about that guy?
Yeah, I guess so.
Don't see many people
with faces like that.
Makes me wanna
get a better look.
[sighs]
Kid.
Take it from me,
I've been here for a while.
The first thing you need to
learn about this place is...
stay the hell away
from Nopperabo.
♪
[whistling]
They move him around.
Every single day, they transfer
him to a different cell.
If we can detect
any kind of pattern
to the way
they're moving him,
we may be able to predict
where he'll be in a few days.
[sighs]
[KID]
Hmm? So this is a pig farm, huh?
There are a bunch of crates
piled in back there.
I need you to go
pile them outside.
Sure, no problem.
-New kid.
-[gasps]
Leave your katana here with me.
If you happen to trip over it,
you'll only end up
covered in pig shit.
Oh, thanks.
[pig grunts]
[KID] Hey, where are
those crates, again?
Chief Kadokura?
[INUDOU] So that new kid
is working with the Seventh?
Well, that's
very interesting, indeed.
I want you to take care of him.
Security Chief Kadokura.
You're saying you want me
to do it myself?
No, you can use the prisoners.
You've got a jail full of people
who are good at murder.
This is my prison
and I run it my way.
Anybody who tries
to mess with me,
will be reduced
to a pile of pig food.
[KADOKURA] Sorry, new kid,
but I don't have a choice.
Hmm.
[gasps]
[grunting]
[KID]
Um...
Chief Kadokura?
♪
[heavy breathing]
Uh, need some help here!
Chief Kadokura?!
It's gone.
My katana.
[gasps]
[grunting]
♪
[gasps]
Oh, Chief Kadokura?
[KADOKURA]
You've gotta be kidding me.
This kid is unbelievably strong.
Forget this, I don't pick fights
I can't win.
[KADOKURA]
Well, it's done.
I fed him to the pigs,
as you instructed.
He fought harder
than I expected,
and he was badly wounded,
so were both prisoners.
In fact, in the end, I just had
to finish off all three.
I reported the new kid
as missing
and the other two
as having died after a brawl.
Seems believable.
When'd you get here?
Seven years ago?
Does that sound about right?
Yes, sir.
I always thought of you
as a wimpy tanuki of a man,
with limp, flaccid balls.
I assumed if I looked up
"useless" in the dictionary,
I'd see your face.
However, today it appears
I'm going to have to
adjust my opinion of you.
Just a little bit.
Thank you very much, sir.
I will never forget this.
Well, this is sad.
I had a lot more research
to do here.
I woefully underestimated
Chief Kadokura.
Lieutenant Tsurumi
is going to scold me!
-[ticking]
-Huh?
What is that noise?
-[neighing]
-[groans]
Oh! Damn it,
I can't see a thing!
Where are they?
[ticking continues]
[MAN]
Leave the horses and the money.
[screaming]
[grunts]
♪
[NARRATOR] Next time,
"The Sound of an Ambush."