♪
My name is Shirosuke Inudou.
Warden of Abashiri Prison.
Nice to meet you.
Inudou.
[gasps]
Uh, who might your friend be?
[SUZUKAWA]
Sugimoto, my guard.
Five years ago,
a brutal criminal
unfortunately bit off his face
in a savage attack.
He may look
a little bit different,
but he's still
very good at his job.
Inudou!
Uh... I'm sorry to hear that.
I can't believe
that actually worked.
I was told Yoshitake Shiraishi
was being held here.
I've come because I want him
sent back to Abashiri.
Shiraishi?
I'm not aware of a prisoner
by that name here.
[YODOGAWA]
Where did he find out?
Who the hell told him?
Do you dare to lie to my face?!
[SUGIMOTO moaning]
Inudou.
[sighs]
[SUZUKAWA clears throat]
Not only did you dare
to illegally transport prisoners
from Abashiri
during my absence,
you then quite stupidly
allowed all of them to escape.
You've made an incredible mess.
Now I'm here.
I came to here to clean up
the idiotic muddle
the Seventh has created.
Regiment Commander.
[gasping]
Contact Lieutenant Tsurumi
in Otaru, now.
♪
So, there's a man
calling himself
Shirosuke Inudou
in Asahikawa, huh?
[chuckles]
[YODOGAWA gasps]
I don't understand.
What are you planning
to do with this?
Do you think I'll accept a bribe
for Yoshitake Shiraishi?
[SUZUKAWA]
That's not what this is.
-The bills are fake.
-Huh?
Look at this. It's the plate
used to make them.
We confiscated it from a genius
counterfeiter whom we arrested.
Look at that work.
Do you know anything
about the Continental dollar
during the American Revolution?
Or Napoleon's
counterfeit gulden?
Spreading counterfeit currency
in a time of war
to cause economic chaos
is an extremely
effective measure.
I have no doubt
this man would be able
to make an accurate copy
of any nation's currency.
I happen to think he could be
quite a valuable asset
to the Japanese Army
in the future.
What do you say? You interested?
[groans quietly]
[SUGIMOTO scoffs]
I thought this guy was just
some washed-up fraudster.
Now I see why Hijikata kept him
as a secret weapon.
Kiyohiro Suzukawa's
no ordinary con artist.
Just one more push
and the Lieutenant Colonel
will give in.
I'm proposing a trade,
the counterfeiter
for Shiraishi.
Lieutenant Colonel Yodogawa.
I can't help noticing that
since the Russo-Japanese War,
every other lieutenant colonel
is made full colonel.
Except for you.
Which seems like
such a terrible injustice.
Don't you believe
you're being treated unfairly?
[gasps]
[SUZUKAWA]
Listen to me.
This will be your path
to promotion.
[gasping]
[OPERATOR]
You've reached the switchboard.
Local or long distance, please?
[TSURUMI over phone]
Long-distance!
Get me the Seventh Division
in Asahikawa.
Regiment 27!
It's me.
Do not go along with
Lieutenant Colonel Yodogawa.
Don't let anyone
see Shiraishi, understand?
Believe me, if Inudou were to
take one step out of Abashiri,
I would obviously
know about it
because my men there
would tell me...
You're too close
to the receiver, sir.
[TSURUMI]
Send Second Lieutenant Koito!
Oh, hell.
That can't be a good thing.
That's one of
Lieutenant Tsurumi's
favorite Satsuma messengers.
Huh?
What is this?
What's going on?
[SUZUKAWA] I have one of my men
waiting out front
with the counterfeiter.
Let's do the exchange outside.
I'm sure you can understand
how we might have
a few trust issues
after the incident
at Abashiri.
[SHIRAISHI]
Oh, my God.
The likeness is pretty uncanny,
but this guy
isn't really Inudou.
Based on the height and build
and the way his clothes hang,
I'd say the weirdo is Sugimoto.
They really came here
to get me back?
-[door opens]
-[gasps]
♪
What is it,
Lieutenant Koito?
I've come with a message
from Lieutenant Tsurumi.
He demands that no one
make contact with Shiraishi
until he himself arrives.
[SUGIMOTO]
Not good. He works for Tsurumi?
And are you under any obligation
to obey the lieutenant's orders?
Lieutenant Colonel?
[moaning]
Get out.
You have no business here.
[KOITO]
Inudou.
[speaking in Satsuma dialect]
Chinchin what?
-[SUZUKAWA grunts]
-[SUGIMOTO moaning]
Forgive me. I've heard it said
that during his time
as the warden of Kabato Prison
in Tsukigata,
Inudou spent a lot of time
with prisoners from Satsuma.
I was led to believe
that he's able to speak
the Satsuma dialect very well.
Koito, what the hell
are you doing?
[speaking in Satsuma dialect]
[grunts]
[gasps]
[sighs]
[speaking in Satsuma dialect]
[SUGIMOTO]
Okay, yeah, he's a genius.
I can't believe
he mastered that so quickly.
[speaking in Satsuma dialect]
[clears throat]
[SHIRAISHI]
This is nuts.
What are they saying
to each other?
Are they really both
speaking Japanese?
[speaking in Satsuma dialect]
[groaning]
[grunts]
According to Lieutenant Tsurumi,
Inudou couldn't drink, at all.
[gasping]
You bastards tried to fool me?!
I should've thrown this idiot
right into the damn river.
Please don't do that!
You're not to hurt Shiraishi.
Tsurumi will kill you.
And by you, I mean me.
[grunts]
Sugimoto!
I'm still Immortal Sugimoto,
rat bastards!
[yelling]
-After them!
-Yes, sir!
-[gunshot]
-[groans]
They have men outside.
-[grunting] Man, that smarts.
-This way, Shiraishi.
Kiroranke and the others
have horses waiting.
[panting]
[SHIRAISHI]
Sugimoto, are you gonna be okay?
[SUGIMOTO]
You have to run!
Stop them!
Sugimoto, this way's bad.
Run to the south. That way!
Unluckily for us, those gunshots
frightened the bees
right out of their hives.
[panting]
[gasps]
Sugimoto was hit pretty badly!
Good thing he's immortal.
You run or you die.
Are you kidding? He's hurt.
He needs help.
He can't just keep
running indefinitely.
[SUGIMOTO]
Shiraishi.
If I don't make it,
then it's up to you
to get Asirpa
to Abashiri Prison, understand?
Uh... [sighs]
♪
[panting]
[gasps]
♪
What the bloody hell is that?
Prototype for a hot air balloon.
Hmm. That's it.
We're stealing that balloon.
[clamoring]
Everyone, get back.
Further back than that.
[grunts]
Give it to me!
Come on, I said hurry up.
Get it going.
[SUGIMOTO]
Get back. We'll shoot!
You can't shoot, you idiot!
You might ignite the hydrogen.
Get 'em down!
[clamoring]
Would you get the hell
off of it, damn you?
♪
Hey. Get back here
with my sword!
[grunting]
[gasping]
[grunts]
Hmm.
Second Lieutenant.
[HIJIKATA]
What is that thing?
Sugimoto's group is on it.
Those gunshots we heard
were from them after all.
They're using it to escape!
♪
I'll handle it.
Bayonet.
He uses Satsuma swordsmanship.
Jigen style.
There's no way you can fight him
with two bullets inside of you.
[gasps]
[KOITO]
Hyakunosuke Ogata. You traitor!
[speaking in Satsuma dialect]
Yeah, sorry, but as usual,
I have no idea
what you're saying right now,
Second Lieutenant Koito.
Have you ever noticed
that when you get upset,
you talk really fast?
[speaking in Satsuma dialect]
[grunts]
Don't block it.
[yelling]
[screaming]
[gasps]
What's he doing?
[grunts]
Shiraishi!
♪
[speaking in Satsuma dialect]
[laughing]
Bye-bye, crazy Koito.
[SUGIMOTO] Shiraishi, you're
about to slam into the trees!
[gasps]
[groaning]
Asirpa!
♪
[sighs]
[speaking in Satsuma dialect]
One of the bullets
passed through your shoulder,
but the other one
is still in your left breast.
We'll need to get
that out later.
I can't believe you were willing
to take that kind of risk
to get me back again.
I mean, I'm the Escape King.
I could've gotten away myself.
Everyone else was
going to give up on you.
The one who insisted
that we didn't was Sugimoto.
Ah!
Is that true?
[SUGIMOTO] You'll help us
when we get to Abashiri.
I know you will.
I believe in you.
That's why I decided
to save you.
But I did remember something,
Shiraishi.
That strange old man we met at
the herring fishery longhouse.
[gasps]
Just admit it.
You were working with Hijikata.
[shuddering]
♪
[SUGIMOTO]
Wait. Don't run!
Look at this.
[gasps]
Isn't that...
[SUGIMOTO] The copy of
Kazou Henmi's tattoos
that you gave to Ushiyama
in Sapporo.
Toshizou Hijikata
showed it to me.
I took a careful look...
and it was a fake.
The truth is,
Shiraishi never betrayed us.
Yes, that's absolutely right!
What did I tell you?
I said I'll always
bet on you, my friend.
[sputtering]
Hey. This thing's
acting really weird.
-[SHIRAISHI grunting]
-[clanging]
-[ASIRPA grunting]
[OGATA]
Would you stop it?
[SHIRAISHI exclaiming]
Guys, you might wanna
look at this!
This is bad.
Pawci casi.
Quite simply, it means "village
where the Pawci-Kamuy live."
It's believed to be the fortress
of the Pawci-Kamuy.
The Pawci are sex demons,
and they're not very good gods.
It's said anyone they possess
will strip off their clothes
and start dancing.
[laughing]
That's so ridiculous!
The Ainu have some
big imaginations, don't they?
[SUGIMOTO]
We're about 40 kilometers away
from the Seventh Division's
barracks.
[OGATA] I saw soldiers on horses
following us from the air.
That thing's not
exactly hard to spot.
They should know
about where we are.
If we don't hurry,
they'll catch up to us.
First, we need
to treat Sugimoto.
I found some retannoya,
or alpine yarrow.
Put the crushed leaves
on the wound
and it stops the bleeding.
Koito only shot me
with a Type 26 revolver.
If you shoot that gun
at a pig's nose
it'll just bounce off.
It's incredibly weak.
Nobody could kill me
with something like that.
But Suzukawa was weaker
than a pig's nose.
[gasps]
Did Suzukawa not make it?
Ah!
♪
[gasps]
They found us.
-[ALL gasp]
-Hurry!
We need to cross
the Daisetsuzan.
Are you being serious?
These mountains are huge!
[wind gushing]
What do we do?
The weather just changed
so quickly.
Why is this wind so cold?
It'll only get stronger.
And it'll rain, too.
We have to go back!
Don't be stupid.
They're still following us.
[SHIRAISHI] Do we dig a hole
in the snow and hide?
[ASIRPA] No. There's not enough
snow left to do it.
[SHIRAISHI exhales]
[laughs]
Shiraishi's acting strange.
Look for a place
to hide from the wind.
Or you'll die of hypothermia.
Yuk. Sugimoto.
Shoot the bucks.
We're gonna need
three of the big ones.
You want me to shoot the deer?
♪
Two at the same time?
[gunshot]
Hurry and skin them fast!
Don't worry how well.
We're gonna hide
inside the deer's bodies.
We're crawling
inside corpses?
[SHIRAISHI laughing]
Pawci Kamuy got him good.
He's gone batty.
-Shiraish--
-Stand still!
You can't run with that wound.
You and Ogata need
to skin the deer.
[SUGIMOTO]
Shiraishi?
[gasps]
But Asirpa's still...
-[grunting]
-Hey, Sugimoto!
You're so pretty and soft
and warm and...
♪
Asirpa!
Hey, Asirpa!
Come on, where are you?
[ASIRPA]
Sugimoto!
[gasps]
[ASIRPA]
Sugimoto!
♪
[BOTH panting]
I lost Shiraishi.
No, he came back.
Huh? Oh, thank goodness.
Listen, are you okay?
You look pale.
Yes, I'm fine. What about you?
We need to head back.
♪
Sugimoto!
Why didn't you shoot?
This deer is me.
♪
[gunshot]
[exhales]
Is your wound bothering you?
No. I'm okay.
It's gonna be better
by tomorrow morning.
Suzukawa. Did he suffer?
How did he die?
Asirpa, Suzukawa was a bad man.
Bad men don't have human hearts.
So they feel less pain
than normal people.
You don't need to
feel sorry for them.
Are you making fun of me
because I'm a kid?
Don't try to feed me
that stuff.
No, it's what
I've tried to think.
During the war,
I would say that
the enemies weren't like us.
That they didn't
suffer as they died.
On the battlefield
your old self dies.
You become someone else
in order to keep fighting.
-[shouting]
-[groaning]
[explosion]
[panting]
[screaming]
[SUGIMOTO] Destroying the person
you once were,
is the only way to survive.
But then, could anybody
go back to who they were?
I have no doubt some people did.
They went back home.
Maybe they were able
to get their old selves back
spending time
with their families.
But those who couldn't
return to themselves
after coming back to Japan,
their hearts are still
on the battlefield.
[ASIRPA chomping]
[SUGIMOTO]
Hmm?
Asirpa. what are you eating?
It's deer liver.
You should have some, too.
You lost a lot of blood today.
I really wanna eat
the brains, too,
but we'll have to wait
till the wind stops.
You really appreciate
a good brain, don't you, Asirpa?
You know I do.
What you do love besides osoma?
You mean food?
Dried persimmons, I guess.
What is that?
That's right, there aren't
any persimmon trees in Hokkaido.
You just take bitter persimmons
and dry them out.
After you dry 'em,
they become sweet.
I haven't had one
for several years.
Before I left for the war,
that was the last time.
Why didn't you have one
when you finally got back
from the fighting?
It was spring.
There weren't any.
[ASIRPA]
I see.
Do you think maybe
if you eat dried persimmons,
you might go back to being
the same person
you were before the war?
♪
[sniffles quietly]
Once all of this is over,
you'll have to take me
to your homeland with you.
That's all I want.
Just to try
some dried persimmons.
That a deal?
Sugimoto?
[NARRATOR]
Next Time, "Ani Nekko."