[birds chirping]
[OGATA] Looks like
they're nowhere near us.
This is probably too optimistic,
but maybe that weather
was too much for the Seventh.
I can't see them giving up
and going home, though, can you?
No, they're expecting us.
They think we'll head down
the mountains towards Abashiri.
So we'll do the unexpected
and head towards
Tokachi to shake them off.
[ASIRPA]
Let's go.
The others know what to do.
If separated,
we meet up in Abashiri.
I sent Huci a telegram.
I wanted to check in with her
and make sure everything
there was all right.
There should be an answer
waiting for us
at this post office.
Who from?
From Asirpa's uncle.
He used to work
with the Japanese for a time,
so he knows how to read
and write a little.
[CIKIAPASI]
What does it say?
"Huci making raikurushiyuku."
What's "raikurushiyuku"?
[INKARMAT]
Raykur Siyuk.
It's a burial shroud.
Hmm.
[INKARMAT]
When an elderly Ainu knows
that death is drawing near,
they prepare their own
burial shroud.
In secret.
Why did you have to say
what you did?
I had no choice but to tell her
what the spirits told me.
There is a traitor
close to Asirpa.
[sighs]
[CIKIAPASI]
I don't want Huci to die.
She took me in and fed me
when I needed it.
She said the Ainu
always care for children.
She says that without them,
you can't move on
to the next world.
Because when an Ainu dies,
those left behind perform
a ritual for their souls.
Otherwise they can't enter
the afterlife.
So they'll take in
and raise any child,
even if they aren't their own.
♪
[TANIGAKI]
Cikapasi, don't worry.
I'm gonna bring Asirpa back
safe and sound.
That'll raise Huci's spirits.
So I won't rest until it's done.
She took me in, same as you.
So I'm one of her kids, too.
No way.
You're her gigolo,
Tanigaki Nispa.
-He sure is.
-[BOTH laughing]
[BOTH sigh]
♪
[TANIGAKI] Maybe this is
what I've been looking for.
[TANIGAKI]
Lieutenant Tsurumi.
Have you ever heard of a food
called kanemochi?
It's an emergency ration
we Ani Matagi use.
One's shaped like a ball
and one's an oval.
We take them into
the mountains with us.
Supposedly,
the round one is the sun
and the oval is the moon.
Kanemochi, huh?
No, I can't say
I've heard of it.
How's it taste?
Like any other mochi?
[TANIGAKI]
We add water to rice powder,
then mix in miso or salt.
Knead thoroughly,
wrap it up in a leaf,
then bake it in a covered pan.
Tozawa Matagi, however,
are forbidden from adding miso
to their kanemochi.
[TSURUMI]
So each village
has its own
particular rules, then?
My father was incredibly stern,
so I never told anybody
about this.
But I didn't actually
follow the rules.
I did something special
to my kanemochi.
Then one day, another Matagi
discovered my secret.
[laughs]
How'd he do that?
That's kind of a story.
We were hunting a wild goat
that we call an "aoshishi."
Matagi travel in small groups
and each member has a specific
role to play in the hunt.
There's a scout, a mukaimatte,
who gives orders to the group.
Then, two riflemen
called matsumai.
And two seko who aren't
allowed to use guns.
The seko's main job
is to be loud
and drive the prey
into the riflemen's sights.
Hyah! Hyah!
[TANIGAKI] The bears the Matagi
call "itazu" have a tendency
to run uphill
into the mountains.
So the seko drive them
toward the peak.
The aoshishi are the opposite,
so we drive them away
from the peaks.
I was a seko, out with a boy
a year older than me
named Kenkichi Aoyama.
When we got up to the peak,
the weather suddenly changed.
♪
We sought refuge in a cave,
but the blizzard kept raging.
We were trapped there for days.
The beans and rice
we'd brought weren't enough.
They ran out fast.
Kanemochi was created
to keep you alive
in situations like that.
No matter how cold it gets,
it doesn't freeze,
and it never spoils.
And nibbling on just a little
of it is enough to fill you up.
[wind howling]
Here.
[scoffs]
What's wrong?
I was just thinking that
if this blizzard doesn't stop,
this could be our last meal.
Ha! Speak for yourself.
I'm surviving this even if
it means I have to eat you.
Hey, what's that taste?
Did you mix something in?
[gasps]
The flavor's familiar.
-Uh--
-Wait.
Don't tell me. I'll guess it.
Uh, let's see.
I know.
It's walnuts.
You put walnuts in, didn't you?
Yeah, but do me favor.
Don't tell my father, okay?
[laughing]
-Hey, Genjirou.
-Huh?
We're going to get
out of this alive.
Hmm.
[TANIGAKI]
Not too long after that,
Kenkichi married
my younger sister, Fumi.
So then, we were like
real brothers.
Mm-hmm.
[TANIGAKI] Fumi and Kenkichi
lived quietly and happily,
just a little ways
up the mountain, on their own.
Away from the village.
[grunting]
On that day,
I'd been making kanemochi
at home as usual.
My brother came in from outside,
with a look on his face
I'd never seen before.
-[footsteps approaching]
-Hmm?
[MAN]
It's Fumi.
[TANIGAKI] When I saw
the sheer panic in his eyes,
it felt like I'd been stabbed
through the chest.
[TANIGAKI panting]
By the time I arrived,
the little hut where the two
of them lived was already...
[panting]
♪
I found her body inside.
It was burned to a crisp.
But why?
[pants]
What happened here?
What the hell happened here?!
Fumi!
That's when I saw
the stab wound in her heart.
♪
And next to her,
Kenkichi's masuke.
The short blade we call a masuke
is the soul of a Matagi.
But Kenkichi wasn't there.
He was nowhere to be found.
Where the hell is he?!
I swear, our son
hasn't been here.
-Please don't hurt us.
-[WOMAN crying]
You're not hiding him, are you?!
[crying]
I searched for him everywhere,
but I never found him.
And then one day,
I finally heard a rumor
that he'd joined the Seventh
in Hokkaido, and I was ready.
[TANIGAKI'S FATHER]
Give it up, Genjirou.
Don't abandon
Ani simply for revenge.
Do you really want to waste
your life like that?
[grunting]
I refuse to let
my sister's murderer live!
Forget being a Matagi, then.
I won't be back.
There were a total
of 37 Tondenhei villages
in Hokkaido at that point.
Between my training
and farm work,
it was easy to move around
and search for Kenkichi.
But I had no luck.
Then, just before
we left for war,
my brother sent me a message
saying my mother was dead.
Fumi's brutal death.
Me abandoning my home
to go to war.
These things were too much
for her frail heart.
She became sick and died.
My hatred grew as I told myself
Kenkichi was responsible
for everything.
If I went to Port Arthur,
where the Hokkaido soldiers
were gathered, I could find him.
Once I had, I'd wait
for my chance in battle...
and shoot him from behind.
[yelling]
[grunts]
[sighs]
[TANIGAKI]
I saw a haggard-looking man
sitting in the corner
of one of the trenches.
His face was so covered
in blood,
whether it was his
or an enemy's was hard to tell.
A white sash.
This man must be a survivor
of last night's suicide charge.
That's impressive.
Hey, man, any chance
you got food?
[gasps]
Um, yeah.
Eat.
I appreciate it.
Thanks a lot.
This firm texture.
Could it be mochi?
And I taste miso.
So what is this,
some kind of Akita dish?
How did you know that?
Not hard to deduce.
Dead giveaway?
The use of these spices.
It's definitely an Akita thing.
There was a private
in the First Division,
where I'm from, who came from
a place called Ani in Akita.
He talked about it all the time.
He told me that he had been
a hunter back home
before he came to Tokyo.
[TANIGAKI]
It was Kenkichi.
I'd finally found
my sister's killer.
That's what had happened.
He'd gone to Tokyo
rather than Hokkaido.
The soldiers at 203 Hill
were from everywhere,
many hailed from
the Hokkaido Seventh,
as well as the Shikoku Eleventh,
also the Kanazawa Ninth.
And, yes, there were many
from the Tokyo first.
[TANIGAKI]
Yes, and the way I saw it,
the gods had finally
helped me discover
my little sister's killer.
That's how it felt.
I wanted to go
and find him immediately,
but I knew that if I saw him,
I'd most likely lose control.
I had a good plan.
I knew I could satisfy my need
for revenge
in the heat of a battle,
where I wouldn't be caught.
But you were there.
That hill was a nightmare.
[SOLDIERS yelling]
[TANIGAKI]
No time to look for anybody
when it's all you can do
just to survive.
[gunfire]
♪
The Russians threw
grenades at us.
And we threw them right back.
[grunting]
[TANIGAKI] As we began to push
them back further and further,
They got desperate
and changed tactics.
Strapped grenades
to their bodies
and jumped in our trenches.
It was hell. I remember.
Blood and body parts everywhere.
Just one of them
could take out ten of us.
[TANIGAKI]
And then, another came.
Bring that man down!
Two hits from a Type 30
right to the chest.
Didn't even slow him down.
[gasps]
Suddenly, a lone man emerged,
running out
of one of the trenches.
[inaudible]
[TANIGAKI]
Kenkichi!
[grunting]
[gasps]
[TANIGAKI]
It was bad.
Kenkichi just barely survived.
At last,
the moment I'd been
waiting for had arrived.
Or so I thought.
Kenkichi.
I've finally found you.
I'm gonna stab you
straight through your heart.
Just like you did to Fumi!
Tanigaki!
Come on, he's done for!
He can't even hear you.
His eardrums were
probably destroyed.
[heavy breathing]
[gasping]
[weakly]
Fumi.
Huh?
[TANIGAKI] The battle seemed
to reach some kind of stalemate,
and the whole place
became strangely quiet.
Why?
Tell me!
Why did you kill Fumi?
[weakly]
Who-who are you?
What's that voice?
I don't know who you are,
but can you take a message?
Can you do that for me?
A man named Tanigaki in Ani.
[gasps]
My brother.
I married the Tanigaki
family's daughter, Fumi.
She was so beautiful.
Such a warm heart.
Far too good for me.
The two of us lived quietly
together in the mountains.
Then one day,
she became sick with smallpox.
[gasps]
My parents.
Don't tell them.
I'm begging you.
Fumi.
If you do, they'll just worry.
And then they'll try
to come here.
If it spreads to them...
I know.
And you.
You can't stay here, either.
Wha...
What are you trying to say?
We'll die together, I swear.
When a member of a mountain
family catches smallpox,
we abandon that loved one
so it won't spread.
But I couldn't.
I couldn't do it.
I'd heard an awful story
about animals finding their way
into an abandoned home
and killing the sick
who were left inside.
I knew there was no way
I'd let her die alone
in that house.
But she refused
to let me stay with her.
If it was known that a Tanigaki
had gotten smallpox,
the rest of the village
would shun them.
The other Matagi
would refuse to hunt
with the rest of her family.
She wanted me to kill her
then leave without telling
anyone in the village.
So...
[crying quietly]
[KENKICHI] She covered
her beautiful face with a cloth,
and then, she said...
If it doesn't spread to you...
[KENKICHI and FUMI]
...then, you must decide.
[FUMI] How to spend
the rest of your life.
Find your role, love.
I'll try.
At last, I finally did it.
We decided on a way for her
to suffer as little as possible.
I am a hunter.
So I used the method
I knew best.
♪
I did what she said.
Burned down our home,
and left the village
without telling her family
about her death.
Ever since,
I've spent the rest of my life
bearing the guilt.
My actions have caused
great pain
to her family
and to the village.
If I can heal those wounds
in any way...
Please, sir.
Please, tell this story
to Tanigaki in Ani.
Please.
♪
[gasps]
Kanemochi with walnuts.
Genjirou.
[TANIGAKI] And then, he passed
from this life before my eyes.
He had found his role in life
and spent the rest of his days
carrying it out.
Every day since, I ask myself
the same question,
"What is my role in life?"
I can't go back to Ani now.
I couldn't bear to face
my father or brother.
Tanigaki.
Perhaps I can help you
answer your question.
Hmm?
Hey, I know what you can do
for a start.
How about some of those
kanemochi with walnuts?
At your service, sir.
[birds squawking]
-[CIKIAPASI] Hey, look at that.
-Hmm?
Somebody's dancing
all the way out there.
Doesn't it look like Asirpa?
Hmm.
Nice.
This is a dance
from Kushiro, right?
[ASIRPA]
The sarorunrimse.
The crane dance.
Hmm. Look, someone's coming.
Uh...
[gasps]
You see?
I knew it, it's Asirpa!
[ASIRPA]
Cikapasi and Cironnup.
And Tanigaki.
How in the world?
[NARRATOR]
Next Time, "Kamuy Hopunire."