[CIKAPASI]
We finally found you!
We've been looking all over
for you since Otaru.
You have been?
[ALL]
Huh?
Yeah, we even met a couple
Ainu hunters over there
and asked if they'd seen you.
♪
Hey. Have either of you seen
an Ainu girl around here?
[BOTH]
Hmm?
She'd most likely be traveling
with a Japanese man
with a scar on his face.
Oh.
Sounds like the one we just saw.
[gasps]
They both seemed
really impressed
that you'd been able
to make it all this way.
They even invited us to come
visit their kotan.
And they just hunted a bear.
-So you know what that means.
-[gasps]
Right, let's go.
There's bear stew
waiting for us all.
If I'm being honest,
I'd much rather go hit
the local bars
with Inkarmat's money.
Leave her alone.
You can't treat her like that,
she's a part of my family.
-[ASIRPA sighs]
-Your what now?
Yeah. She's nice to me
and looks after me
and she doesn't get mad
when I touch her boobs.
And Tanigaki Nispa
is her gigolo.
That is correct.
[TANIGAKI]
What are they doing here?
Gigolo?
[TANIGAKI]
Um, no.
[singing in Ainu]
[children chuckling]
Hmm?
So, you found them.
Glad you made it.
[HUNTER 1]
Just in time.
The Kamuy Hopunire's
about to start.
[HUNTER 2]
Enjoy yourselves.
It's a ceremony, and it means
"The Setting-Off of Gods."
So they send off the spirit
of the hunted bear.
It's a different ritual
than an iomante,
where they send off a bear
that was raised in a cage.
[MAN]
Oh-oh-oh-hoy!
Ah-ah-ah-hoy!
That's called an "okokokse."
They shout out to tell
the god of fire about the bear.
The kamuy are the things
beyond human control.
Some things help us,
other things bring us disaster.
Fire is a critical part
of our lives,
and blades slice
cleanly through things
we can't cut on our own.
So they have kamuy in them.
Trees are kamuy
that sit on the mountains.
Bad weather and plague
are beyond human control,
so they're kamuy, too.
But it's not that we believe
these things are any greater
than humanity.
We think of them
as equals to us.
We believe that when hunting,
it's not the arrows
hitting our prey,
it's the kamuy
running into them.
We invite them to our world,
and in exchange
for their meat and pelts,
they ask for sake and tobacco.
Things that only we can make.
Then we send off the kamuy
with a proper ritual.
In the hopes they'll tell
the other kamuy
the human world
is a good place for them to go.
If we don't treat them properly,
they'll never come back
to our world.
After this, the bear's head will
be taken to an outdoor altar
decorated with inaw.
Inaw are shaven sticks
that we give
to the kamuy as an offering.
Over time,
as it collects inaw,
its status
in its own world grows.
It's said that the inaw
we give it
transform into silver and gold,
becoming valuable treasures.
Even in the afterlife,
we're driven by gold.
Somehow, I'd hoped we'd be
better than that by then.
♪
[indistinct chatter]
Will you stay here long?
Well, that's not
really up to me.
[SHIRAISHI groaning]
That's delicious.
[chuckles softly]
[ASIRPA]
What's she thinking?
I wonder.
[TANIGAKI]
Asirpa.
There's something
I need to tell you.
I've come
because I have news about Huci.
[snoring]
[ASIRPA]
Huci.
So we're really supposed
to believe
that you came all the way
from Otaru
just to tell her that,
Private Tanigaki?
Something you wanna say?
How about
if we don't play games?
I know Tsurumi sent you here
just to watch me.
No, you're wrong.
I'm done with the Seventh,
with the whole army.
That old lady helped me out,
so I'm here
for her granddaughter.
It's as simple as that.
Not sure I believe you.
You were one of Tsurumi's
most fervent followers
and you even killed three men
in the mountains, as I recall.
Hmm...
In the mountains?
You're talking about the three
he was traveling with?
If so, it was a bear
that killed them.
I was there and I saw it.
So I'm sure.
A bear?
Hmm.
So the old lady just had a dream
where she never saw
her granddaughter again?
It was just a dream.
You could've sent a damn letter.
[ASIRPA]
We Ainu believe
dreams are things the kamuy send
when they're trying
to communicate.
When they have something
to show us.
I don't believe that now,
but Huci is one of the old Ainu.
And once, long ago,
she had another dream.
In this dream, her daughter
was surrounded by bears.
They were sending her off
to the next world.
According to Huci,
soon after that,
my mother got sick and died.
So that's why she always
believes her dreams.
-Listen, Asirpa.
-Hmm?
Do you just wanna head back?
If she sees your face,
then surely that takes her dream
out of the "prophecy" category,
doesn't it?
She'll feel better.
Don't force yourself to stay.
[gasps]
[sighs]
Don't treat me like a child,
Sugimoto.
I can't stop.
I have to keep going now.
I need to find the truth,
then move forward
for the sake of my own dream.
♪
[snoring]
Hey. Tanigaki Nispa.
I've been wondering.
That Murata gun,
did it belong to Tetsuzou Nihei?
[gasps]
How did you know Nihei?
We hunted bears together.
Over a decade ago.
He was so good at it.
I'm still amazed there were
any bears left on that mountain.
He died in those mountains.
He had his gun on him.
I couldn't leave it.
I would've done the same thing.
Although, it must be challenging
using an old gun like that.
Nihei changed me.
From a soldier
back into a Matagi.
I decided to carry it
so I'll never forget
how to feel
when I shoot my prey.
"You get one shot, so do it
right the first time." Right?
[scoffs]
See that on the barrel?
Those seven little marks
he scratched out?
Nihei once told me
what they meant.
I've got a lot of kids,
no doubt about it,
but I only ever had one son.
This is the gun
he carried with him
during the first
Sino-Japanese War.
A friend of his gave it to me.
And he told me each mark
on the stock
represented an enemy
my son had shot.
Maybe he just stopped counting
after the seventh.
Or maybe he died shortly after.
Either way, he wasn't the type
who found any joy
shooting people.
He was the kind that'd feel
guilty after killing someone.
Never should've been a soldier.
He should've just stayed home
and shot bears with me.
♪
-[leaves rustling]
-[BOTH] Huh?
Ryu, is that you, boy?
[barking]
Ryu?
[CIKAPASI]
Oh, wow! Look.
Okay, yeah, what's Nihei's dog
doing here?
Did you bring him with you?
Actually, no.
[SUGIMOTO gasps]
Oh, my gosh.
[voice breaking]
Don't tell me.
Have you been following Tanigaki
all this time
because he had Nihei's gun?
♪
[whimpers]
Ryu!
You're the best dog
in the world!
Ow, what the hell?
Stop biting me, stop biting me,
stop biting me, stop biting me.
[grunts]
That hurt, you little shit!
Get lost!
Looks like Ryu's a loyal dog.
He's not quite ready to forget
the enemy of his master.
♪
Tell me.
What are you gonna do now?
I'll leave once she achieves
her goal, and not before.
Understood.
Asirpa.
Once we're in town,
I'll send Huci a telegram.
That would be great.
[chuckling]
Well, off to Abashiri.
Asirpa, ready to go?
Yeah.
[SUGIMOTO]
Oh-oh-oh-hoy!
[KOITO nervously]
Ohh!
Lieutenant Tsurumi
is gonna scold me.
[sighs] He must've been so mad
when he heard
I let Yoshitake Shiraishi
get away.
Uh, how did he look?
Please, Sergeant.
Tell me the truth.
Did Tsurumi say anything
at all about me?
-Uh...
-Don't say it!
I already know!
[crying]
I'm done for.
I'm gonna be sent
straight off to Abashiri
to watch Shirosuke Inudou!
[crying]
Second Lieutenant,
calm yourself.
Look what I have for you here.
I brought you the photos
you asked for.
[gasps]
[KOITO gasps]
These are so wonderful,
Tsukishima.
This must have been taken
before the Battle of Mukden.
He doesn't have those scars
on his face yet.
[sighs]
I'm jealous of you,
Sergeant Tsukishima.
Huh?
Sometimes I think if only
I'd been born a little earlier
then maybe I could've
fought with him, too.
This is so perfect!
Tsukishima, crush up some rice
to use as glue.
No.
I didn't know you were here,
Second Lieutenant.
[screaming]
[TSURUMI]
Hey.
[speaking in Satsuma dialect]
Goodness, calm down.
I can't make out that high-speed
Satsuma dialect,
so why don't you take
some deep breaths and try again?
[inhales and exhales]
[speaking in Satsuma dialect]
Slow down!
Help me!
Tell him that Shiraishi
did get away
but not before I made
a copy of his tattoos.
[sighs]
He says he made a copy
of Shiraishi's tattoos.
Why am I the only one
who gets the high-speed Satsuma
dialect treatment,
Second Lieutenant Koito?
I'll be honest,
I specifically ordered you
not to kill Shiraishi
because I thought he could
be of great value to us.
Yet, you unfortunately let him
fall into enemy hands.
I'm very disappointed in you,
Second Lieutenant.
[groaning]
♪
Oh-oh. A fashion statement
if I ever saw one.
So that's the skin
of the prisoner
pretending to be Inudou.
I'll admit, this is
a lovely unexpected bonus.
From what we've learned so far,
I think it's safe to say
these tattoos
belonged to the con artist,
Kiyohiro Suzukawa.
Very well done,
Second Lieutenant.
However,
the lines aren't quite right.
[shrieks]
Sunmohan! Sunmohan! Sunmohan!
See, this is what I'm talking
about, Second Lieutenant.
[KOITO]
Sunmohan! Sunmohan! Sunmohan!
As of now, you're off
the Asahikawa Mission.
[groaning]
From now on,
you're going to be
personally helping me
hunt the other prisoners.
[gasping]
Eh?
[whispering]
Tell him that I'll do my best.
He said he'll do his best.
He's thrilled.
[HAJIME]
God, I hate this.
Think very carefully
and tell me,
are you absolutely positive
it was Hyakunosuke Ogata
who was aboard the airship
with Shiraishi and Sugimoto?
-[whispers] Yes.
-Yes.
-[whispering] About Ogata...
-About Ogata...
-He brings disgrace...
-He brings great disgrace...
[BOTH] ...to the noble suicide
of his good father,
former head of
the Seventh Division.
-Even my father feels...
-Even my own father feels...
a very strong distrust
towards the Central Command
for the way they handled it.
They blamed it on
the Seventh Division.
So what could Ogata
be thinking in doing this?
I believe that Second Lieutenant
Koito's father
and General Hanazawa
were both born in Satsuma
and that they were friends,
correct?
[KOITO grunts]
The cause of the suicide
was central command
unfairly laying the full blame
for the high casualties
on 203 Hill
at Lieutenant General
Hanazawa's feet.
I, of course, took it
for granted
that Ogata would fight
for his father's honor
and for that of
the Seventh Division.
That was my great mistake.
[OGATA] At the time, my father
was a lieutenant colonel
in the First Imperial
Guard Regiment.
Given his position, he must've
been pretty irritated
to have an Asakusa geisha
bear his child.
Once his wife bore him
a legitimate son,
my grandmother told me
he stopped coming
to visit entirely.
When I was still a baby,
my grandmother took
my mother and me
back to her home in Ibaraki.
My mother used
to make monkfish stew.
Fugu in the west and monkfish
in the east, they'd say.
It was a local dish
for the lower classes.
I liked it and ate it a lot.
In fact, I ate that stew
pretty much constantly.
Every day in winter, my mother
would get up and make more.
Every afternoon,
a new batch of monkfish stew.
My father said he liked it,
so she'd keep making it,
hoping he'd come back
and eat some with her.
Every day, without fail.
She'd gone crazy at this point,
I think.
[gunshot]
One day, I took an old gun
of my grandfather's
out to the field
and I shot a bird.
I thought
maybe if I brought it home,
my mother wouldn't make
that damned stew.
But no matter
how many birds I hunted,
she refused to stop making it.
I couldn't take it anymore.
When my grandparents were gone,
I put rat poison
in the monkfish stew
and fed it to her.
I figured if my father
had any love left for my mother,
he would come to the funeral.
And one more time,
she'd be with the man she loved.
Wouldn't you know?
♪
You never came.
Are you trying to tell me
that this is revenge
for taking off on you two
all those years ago?
All you did was put your
insane mother out of her misery.
You were sick of her, too.
You're no different than me.
[OGATA] Unfortunately,
children don't get
to choose their parents.
Love is as vague and indefinable
a concept as God.
But I think that if you did have
any love for my mother,
you wouldn't have abandoned her.
I've wondered if maybe
a child born to parents
who don't love each other
comes out missing something.
No matter how impressive
his father's bloodline might be.
If you want proof, just look
at your other child,
the true son your wife gave you.
Second Lieutenant
Yuusaku Hanazawa, a nobleman.
We met after I joined
the military,
and I didn't know how to react.
He insisted on calling me
"big brother,"
showing me deference,
no matter how many times
I told him he outranked me.
He never left me alone.
Said his entire life,
he'd wished he had a brother.
[inaudible]
[OGATA]
That innocent smile.
Ohh!
Looking at it, I realized
that this was a boy
who'd grown up feeling safe...
and loved by his parents.
But with all that love
between them,
his father had no way of knowing
the truth about his death.
How his precious son really died
at 203 Hill.
[gunshot]
I shot him in the back
of the head.
Not out of jealousy
or malice of any kind.
Or a desire to make our father
suffer because of his death.
It was more of an experiment,
I guess.
When he heard about
Yuusaku's death,
would our father think of me,
his other son?
Would he suddenly care
about the child he'd had
with his mistress and abandoned
all those years ago?
♪
Was there a chance
I could've been happy, too,
if things had turned out
differently?
♪
Well, you got one thing right.
[labored breathing]
You're missing something
important deep in your core.
You're a failure of a son.
A curse upon you!
♪
[scoffs]
[gasps]
[TSURUMI] Don't worry,
it's all happening as it should.
The brass will make the Seventh
take responsibility
for his suicide.
It'll be a difficult time
for us,
but you're strong,
and you'll endure.
With an external enemy,
I believe that the Seventh will
come together like never before.
In fact, I predict
that they'll very much
want to make
the only surviving son
of Lieutenant General Hanazawa
into a hero.
I think they'll see in you
something of the god of war
they lost.
So, well done,
Hyakunosuke Ogata.
Very well done, indeed, sir.
[OGATA]
Goddamn seducer.
[NARRATOR]
Next time, "Blue Eyes."