(dramatic orchestral music)
(explosion booming) (rumbling)
- [Narrator] Life is theresult of the struggle
between dynamic  opposites, form and chaos
substance and oblivion,light and dark
and all the infinite variations of yin and yang.
When the pendulumswings in favor of one,
it eventually swings back  in favor of its opposite,
and thus the balance of the universe is maintained.
On Earth this balance was disrupted by a nuclear Holocaust,
which rendered technology unless
and devastated the planet's population.
(dramatic orchestral music)
(grand orchestral music)
(soft orchestral music)
(birds chirping)
(explosion booming)
(thunder roaring)
(dramatic music)
Human existence  became a struggle
for uncontaminated  water and food.
Only the strongest survived.
In this age of chaos, men were fearful,
and power over other men made them feel less afraid.
The flame of life on Earth was sputtering,
and if extinguished,  would never be rekindled.
But there were those whose concern was not for themselves
but for their world and its inhabitants.
(wind howling)
(light orchestral music)
- Where can we go from here?
We've been walking for days,
and wherever we look the Earth is barren.
It's a wasteland.
We can't let it end like this.
If we fail all that'll be left is dust.
- Who knows?
(gasping)
(gong blaring)
Shin.
- The time has come.
Julia is mine now.
(dramatic orchestral music)
In times like these only the strongest
may possess what  is most valuable.
- (gasping) What are you doing?
- Let her go.
- Get back.
I warn you don't stand in my way, Ken.
I don't wanna hurt you,but I will if I have to.
You see Julia is  mine, understand?
- This is madness.
The fists of the north and south
aren't ever supposedto fight you know that.
- Perhaps it was true once,
but now rules are meaningless.
Defend yourself, (grunting).
(tense orchestral music)
(soft grunting)
(dramatic orchestral music)
(grunting)
Come, Julia, it's over.
- Oh, I can't leave him now not like this.
Ken, Ken.
Ken.
(dramatic orchestral music)
- Brother, the time has come for us
to teach that bastard Shin a lesson now.
(gasping)
- I've won and you have lost.
The question is why?
Because the power of your will has no ambition to feed it
or the need to crush your enemy.
(grunting)
- Oh, no.
Shin, at one time you  were Ken's closest friend.
He trusted and respected you.
When you were chosen asFist of the South Star,
he was glad for you, glad  for his friend's success.
But you were never really  his friend, were you?
- Yes, I was, but then he left,
and when he came back, he brought you.
The first time I saw you I knew you'd be mine someday,
and that day has come.
- Shin's broken all the rules,
and to think that Ken trusted him like a brother.
But we're his brothers.
You're the strongest, Raoh.
You've got to get down there
and challenge Shin to a fight.
You know you can take him.
Now with Ken out of the way
you will be the Fist of the North Star.
Of course, it's your decision to face him or not,
and I won't blame  you if you don't.
After all, we both  know what happens
if you challenge the power  of the Fist and fail.
You either bleed to death,
become a mindless vegetable or worse.
But I'm certain you're strong enough to win.
Who knows better than me I'm your brother, aren't I?
- [Shin] Believe me I now  how much you love Julia,
but I'm certain that you  want what's best for her.
- [Julia] Ken.
(soft sobbing)
- For instance, you want  her to be safe, don't you?
Look at how you've  protected her.
Under the circumstances,
it's clear that she'll be safer with me.
- I'll never be yours, Shin.
- Julia, you have no choice.
You're mine now.
- Force is the only way you'll get me to leave him.
But I won't ever go of my own free will.
- Oh, perhaps I can change your mind.
(dramatic orchestral music)
(loud screaming)
(soft gasping)
Have you changed your mind yet?
(loud screaming)
- Ken.
- It's up to you, Julia.
Does he live or does he die?
Say it, Julia.
Speak and I'll stop.
Just say you belong to me.
- She knows I'd rather  die than hear that, Shin.
Just as I know that she'd  rather die than say it.
- [Julia] Ken.
- If that's the way youwant it, then so be it.
- [Julia] No!
- I hate to do this to an old friend,
but I'm afraid you've left me no choice.
(loud screaming)
(gasping)
- No, more.
- If you say it.
- No, Julia.
- I'm yours, Shin.
- Louder, much louder.
When you whisper like that,
it's hard for me to believe that you're sincere,
so say it again butthis time with feeling.
Make me a believer, Julia.
(Ken screaming)
- Shin, I'm yours.
I give myself to you with all my heart.
Just don't hurt him again.
It's over, you've won.
(Shin chuckling)
(groaning)
- Did you hear what she just said, Ken.
Fascinating, isn't it,  how changeable woman are?
One minute they  say they want you,
and the next minute they say they want someone else.
That's because they onlywant who they've got
until someone better comes along.
(loud chuckling)
But, of course, she is right.
Julia is tremendously loyal to whomever is the strongest.
I'm afraid you just don't qualify.
- Ken (sobbing).
Ken.
(somber orchestral music)
No.
Ken.
- Come, Julia, it's time to go.
(gasping)
- Julia.
Julia.
- Ken.
I'm sorry.
- He's still breathing.
Think he'll make it?
- Even if he does,  he'll be weak.
The Fist of the North Star  must be strong like me.
- If you're so sure of yourself,
why don't you go after Shin and challenge him right now?
You'll have to face him sooner or later.
- Julia, come back.
She left the seeds.
- These seeds will make the Earth green again someday.
(wind blowing swiftly)
(soft chuckling)
- I hate to admit it, Ken,
but our brother Raoh is right.
You're weak still there's no point in taking any chances.
So now you die.
(loud chuckling)
Sleep well, Ken.
(door creaking)
- Ryuuken, the Fist of the North Star has been defeated.
Shin crushed him as he would an insect.
When you chose Ken  as your successor,
I told you that it  should've been me,
and I was right.
(dramatic orchestral music)
Stand up I'll prove it to you.
I challenge you to a test of strength.
- Physical strength is no  substitute for perception.
For perception is the key
which unlocks the intangible power of the spirit.
You perceive nothing.
- You silly old fool.
Stop hiding behind  your metaphors
and metaphysical fantasies.
The Fist of the North Star is dead.
- Your point?
- Don't you understand now I'm Fist of the North Star.
(loud grunting)
(explosion booming)
(statues crumbling)
My powers are greater than ever before.
No one can stand against me.
- Maybe but you see,
power without perceptionis spiritually useless
and, therefore,  of no true value.
- Useless (chuckling).
Ryuuken, what a foolishold man you are.
Any tool is useful ifyou know how to use it,
and I've become  an expert, watch.
Admit it at this moment
I'm more powerful than you ever were.
I am Fist of the North Star.
- I don't agree,
and I never shall.
Go and do what you must, Raoh,
but never set foot in this dojo again.
(explosion booming)
(wind howling)
(dramatic orchestral music)
(thunder crashing)
- There's no one,
no one as worthy as I am.
(thunder roaring)
(gentle orchestral music)
I am the Fist of the North Star.
(thunder crashing)
Show me the power.
Prove that I'm right.
(thunder roaring)
Yes, show me now.
(dramatic orchestral music)
(soft gasping)
(loud chuckling)
(loud grunting)
- Please.
(blaring heavy metal music)
(grunting)
(engine approaching)
(dramatic orchestral music)
(lively rock music)
- Hey, leave us alone, you son of a bitch.
(loud screaming)
(window shattering)
(grunting)  Holy cow.
(grunting)  Holy shit.
(car crashing) (groaning)
- Hey, took a look.
I knew it.
I told you these two  would have food, didn't I?
I was right.
- Come on stop wasting time.
That buggy's had it.
Whatever village those kids came from
can't be too far from here.
We've gotta go tell Zenda now.
- Maybe it's just alose wire or something.
You're gonna start now you piece of crap, you understand.
(loud chuckling)
- Hey, my car what the, hey.
- What do you know, the kid's still alive.
- Get out of my car, you hear me, hey.
Took the food, every else,
but if you scratch that car,
I'm gonna be forced to kill ya.
(soft chuckling)
- Hey, what do we got here?
Maybe it's jewelry.
Nah, just a bunch of seeds,
a binge of crumby seedsnot worth anything.
(loud grunting)
Ow.
Give me that stick  you little, bitch.
- Let her go, let  her go, you ape.
- Hey, we let these kids go they'll warn the village.
Better get rid of them.
- Right.
You're sure a feistylittle runt, aren't ya?
Sweet dreams, kid.
(dramatic orchestral music)
Huh?
(grunting)
(electronic whirling)
(explosion booming)
What the hell?
(buildings crumbling)
- Wow.
(dramatic orchestral music)
(loud gasping)
- Come on.
(grunting)
(arrow clanking)
(loud screaming)
(whirring)
- Ready.
Now get him.
(loud screaming)
(loud grunting)
(screaming)
- Oh, shit.
(gasping)
(heavy gasping)
(gentle orchestral music)
How did you know we were in trouble?
You couldn't have hard anything, no way.
You were at least  a mile from town.
- Be that as it may Iheard the girl cry out.
- [Bat] That's bullshit.
- Hmm.
- I mean you couldn't have.
Whatever you heard  it wasn't her.
See Lynn's a mute,  can't say a thing.
Our families werefriends before the war,
and she used to talk so much, we called her motor mouth.
But then the war came,
and she was forced to watch
while her folks  were burned alive.
Ever since then she hasn't spoken a word.
Nice kid.
If you hadn't come along today,
I don't know what I would have,
hmm, great, fall asleep why don't ya?
(soft grunting)
(laughing)
- Yeah.
- Let's do it.
(heavy metal music)
(people screaming)
Listen you people, justbring us all your food
and water and we're on our way.
Refuse me and the girl  will be the first to die.
- If we give up, you'll most likely kill us all anyway.
(loud chuckling)
- Maybe so, but if ya don't,
I'll break this kid into pieces
and stuff them down your throat.
(loud grunting)
(spitting)
Who did that?
I dare you to come forward
and show me who you are.
- That's the one, get him.
(grunting)
(dramatic orchestral music)
- Hey, (grunting)
(screaming)
(grunting)
(knuckles cracking)
- Zenda, put her down and let her go.
- Yeah, sure I'll put her down
right after I break her neck.
(loud grunting)
(grunting)
(high pitch tone ringing)
- First you suffer thenyou die nice and slow.
You hear me.
'Cause when I fight,
it's always to the death.
- That's right.
In fact, you're already dead.
- Is that so?
Hmm.
(loud grunting)
(explosion booming)
(people gasping)
- Fist of the North Star.
- Lovely child, pity she can't speak.
Is there nothing you can do for her?
(gentle orchestral music)
- Lynn, is that your name?
My name's Ken.
What I'm about to do mightfeel a little strange at first,
but I promise not to hurt you, all right?
I'm here because you cried out.
Yes, with your mind.
Let it rest now,serene and calm.
(high pitch tone ringing)
- [Bat] Lynn, are you all right?
- Don't worry, she'll  recover in a few moments.
She'll be able to speak now.
- Oh, come on that'd be a miracle.
Are you sure?
- For you, Lynn.
What's inside is as valuable as anything on Earth.
The seeds of new life
I know of only two people
special enough to  make them bloom,
and one of them is you.
- Oh, don't go.
Stay here with us.
- Talk about weird, boy, what an odd ball.
Lynn, you talked.
- Why did he have to go away?
Ken.
Oh, Ken.
(wind howling)
(nunchucks whirling)
(loud grunting)
(grunting)
(laughing)
(gentle orchestral music)
- Hey, I thought you was a girl.
Either way you die.
- Sorry, I don't agree.
I believe you are theone who's about to die.
(high pitch tone ringing)
In fact, there's  no doubt about it.
(men grunting)
(grunting)
Hey, these belong to you?
- Oh, no (screaming).
- Listen, ass wipe, I need some information.
Tell me what I wanna know,
and I'll save your  miserable life,
otherwise you can  bleed to death.
Now tell me
where's the one they call the Fist of the North Star.
(dramatic orchestral music)
- These fools refuse to acknowledge Lord Ken's authority.
Now they're dead.
So, you there doyou live or die?
- Please, oh, please let me go.
- First, you must  show your master
the respect that he deserves.
Bow down to my Lord Ken  the man with seven wounds,
the Fist of the North Star.
- I'll say anything, do anything you want,
just don't kill me.
- See how you've neglected
the statue of your  lord and leader.
Why one might think that this entire village was disloyal.
Now's your chance to convince me of your loyalty.
Tell me, who's your master?
- [Prisoner] The Fist of the North Star.
- Yeah, right, we might  just have a winner folks.
Just one more thing.
All you gotta do is decapitate your friend there.
(gasping)
- Go on.
- Yeah, you heard him.
Just do it.
- [Man] What are you  waiting for an invitation.
(man grunting)
- No, I can't do it, I just can't do it.
- You call that loyalty.
You had your chance,  asshole, and you blew it.
Who needs you.
(women crying)
- Why, why would the man who killed Zenda
and saved our village send these animals here to kill us?
I can't believe the Fist of the North Star
would do such a thing.
- Oh, yeah.
Guess again.
(screaming)
- Who's that guy?
- My name is Rei.
I'm looking for the man you've described,
the man with seven wounds
who calls himself theFist of the North Star.
(grunting)
- All right you.
- Hold it.
I'll give you this much,
you got guts walking in here like this.
Give me that.
So with all due respect,
I'll let you be the oneto cut his head off.
- [Rei] That's quite an honor,
but I'd hate for you to miss all that fun on my account.
You sure about this?
- Hey, what are friends for, right?
(grunting)
Wait a minute, I was talking about the other guy.
- Silly me, what  a foolish mistake.
- I got a splitting headache.
- Oh.
(loud groaning)
Better now.
(men groaning)
Now take me to your boss,
Ken, the man with  the seven wounds,
the Fist of the North Star.
- The hell I will (groaning).
(groaning)
- One question, satisfy my curiosity.
That statue in the town square
who's it suppose to be?
- The Fist of the North Star.
(screaming)
(dramatic orchestral music)
- It's a good likeness,
but it's not the Fist of the North Star.
(grunting)
My brother Jagi always did have a glass jaw.
(dramatic orchestral music)
(soft gasping)
- [Jagi] Shine them perfectly
or I'll make youlick them clean.
- Yes, Lord Jagi.
- [Jagi] Alei,  how dare you speak
to your lord and masterwithout permission.
Such insubordination must be punished.
You disappoint me.
Get up and bring me the whip.
- Jagi is pretending to be me.
He's this man with sevenwounds you've been looking for.
- That may be so,
but I won't know if you're  telling me the truth
until I find him.
- Yes, I understand.
But since we both  wanna find him,
why don't we join  force until we do.
- That's fair enough.
A truce until I know for certain
who's responsible for kidnapping my sister.
Her wedding veil.
She was about to marry
her lifelong sweetheart,Ken, she was so happy.
I'd been away for a while,
and was on my way home when it happened.
Our village was attacked and almost everyone was killed.
It was one of the survivors who told me
that Alei was still alive,
and that the man who'd taken her
had seven wounds and wore an iron mask.
(dramatic tone)
(heavy gasping)
- [Jagi] Ken.
- Not now, Jagi.
- [Jagi] As usual you dismiss me like some
stray dog begging forscraps but not anymore.
- What's the gun for?
If you think you can beat me,
then use your fists.
- [Jagi] You idiot.
I don't care about codes of honor or bullshit philosophy.
I want what's mine and now I'm gonna get it.
(grunting)
- Stop it, you're acting like a fool.
(thudding)
(heavy breathing)
- [Jagi] You're the youngest.
You don't deserve to be fist.
You'll die.
(loud grunting)
(yelling)
(groaning)
I'm gonna rip you in to--
(loud groaning)
(breathing heavily)
- Most of my life I've called you brother.
No more.
(breathing heavily)
- Lord Jagi, the fat one has disappeared.
Lord Jagi.
(breathing heavily)
(suspenseful orchestral music)
(loud screaming)
(gasping)
- Well.
(soft sobbing)
I'm ashamed of you, Jackal.
I didn't think that  anything could scare you,
but it seems I was wrong.
You look like you've seen a ghost or worse.
Do you think I don't know  how disgusting my face is.
You can't even bear to look at me, can you?
- [Jackal] Please, please  my lord forgive me.
I didn't mean to (groaning).
(screaming)
- The scum who don't pay proper respect to their lord
don't deserve to live.
- So this pretender, this  so-call brother of yours
has his hooks into Alei.
- Until we find her.
- [Jagi] So Ken has finally come, has he?
Alei.
- [Alei] Master.
- [Jagi] You mightbecome useful after all.
- How may I serve you, my lord?
(grunting)
(rumbling)
(soft chuckling)
- Well, what have we here?
Why, of course, you mustbe Lord Jagi's brother.
He told me that you'd be showing up sooner or later.
- Good, now get out of my way, pig.
- Nope, I don't think so, not today.
See the boss told me to stop ya,
and nobody gets by me unless I say so.
(grunting)
(soft chuckling)
Hey, what's the matter, little fella
you got your hand stuck.
You're not the first one it's happened to
and you won't be the last.
You see, that's why I'mLord Jagi's bodyguard.
He doesn't like  uninvited guests,
and since you don't have an invitation,
I'm afraid you're gonna have to leave.
(laughing)
Next time call first.
(soft chuckling)
- Need a hand?
- I do appreciate the offer,
but I can handle this guy by myself, thanks.
- Yeah, that's what you think, wise guy.
(loud grunting)
Ha, nice try, guy.
- Say your goodbyes, lard ass, because you're already dead.
(yelling)
- You see?
What did I tell ya?
Still in one piece, good as new.
(screaming)
- Hmm.
A little sloppy but interesting technique.
(heavy breathing)
- Jagi.
- [Jagi] Dear brother, welcome.
(breathing heavily)
- He's the one.
- Allow me to introduce my brother,
the one who killed your  parents and abducted Alei.
- [Jagi] So Alei'sbrother isn't that nice.
A family reunion how touching.
Let the show begin.
(gasping)
- My lord, I am at your command.
What is your wish?
I shall do anything
and everything in my power to please you.
- Alei, no.
Alei.
- Oh, I understand you've  given me to another,
a new master.
As you wish, my lord.
I bid my new master welcome
and promise thatI will serve you
as I have served Lord Jagi.
- Oh, no, Ken she  can't see a thing.
- [Jagi] True, but as a result,
her other senses are more acute.
Her sense of touch for instance.
- You filthy animal.
(dramatic orchestral music)
(gasping)
- [Jagi] You'd kill to get  her back, wouldn't you?
Then do us both a favorand kill my brother,
and your sister will be free to go.
- Rei, you know it's a lie.
- [Jagi] Refuse and your sister will die.
(grunting)
- Jagi's a coward.
He's so afraid of me he has to have others
do his fighting for him.
(chuckling)
- [Jagi] You always were the clever one,
weren't you, brother?
But you cleverness won't do you any good.
I know all your tricks.
I know you think that by calling me a coward
you'll maneuver into making a mistake.
You've made a fool of me all my life but not this time.
Now I hold the winning hand, brother.
- Winning hand, sure and everyone respects a winner, right?
You think anyonewill respect you
for kidnapping a helpless girl and holding her hostage
and using her as a shield to protect yourself from me.
- Everyone will pay heed to Lord Jagi.
They will, I know they will.
(grunting)
- Hey, what the hell.
- [Jagi] But I see your point.
After all, why  should I be robbed
of the pleasure of killing you myself.
The rest of you guard  the girl and her brother.
I'll take care of them later.
- Is that panic I hear in your voice?
Don't worry, it'll  all be over soon.
- [Jagi] Now I'm going to make you suffer like I have.
- What you have suffered is nothing
compared to the suffering  you've caused others.
- You're wrong, brother.
No one has known  pain like I have.
Intense never ending pain and it's all thanks to you.
The only reason I had to  go on living was revenge.
- Jagi, why did youthrow me over the cliff
instead of finishing me off when you had the chance.
- That was a mistake.
I should never have listened to Raoh.
- What do you mean?
- Raoh believed  that you'd been so
badly wounded in your fight with Shin
that you wouldn't recover  or be able to fight again.
Besides killing a  helpless cripple
wouldn't have been much fun,
not nearly as much as I'm going to have now.
(grunting)
- Come on.
(loud grunting)
(groaning)
Go ahead, use your gunif you think it'll help.
- [Jagi] You think I won't, just watch.
- You know, sometimes a blow like that
can affect your muscle control.
If I were you, I'd get rid of that gun.
(grunting)
(gun firing)
- [Jagi] You've changed, haven't you?
You're a lot stronger and trickier too.
But I've got some  tricks of my own.
(laughing)
(explosion booming)
Come on, brother.
Let's see if you're fireproof too.
- Your time has run out.
Farewell, brother.
- (chuckling) But there's  so much you don't know.
Why do you think your old friend, Shin
turned on you and  took your woman?
Didn't you ever wonder about his sudden change of heart?
He once thought that Juliacould never love anyone but you
until I convinced him otherwise.
Julia made me swear not to tell you,
but I want what's best for her.
After all, I love her like  she was my own sister.
In her heart of hearts you're the one she's in love with.
She doesn't care abouthim anymore, believe me.
Besides who's going to protect her.
In times like these only the strongest
can protect the ones they love.
Ken's not as strong as you are.
You're the one who  can keep her safe.
You're the one she loves.
She wants you, Shin.
She wants you with  all her heart.
She belongs to you.
She's yours, so take her,
take her now.
- So it was you all along.
- [Jagi] Clever, wasn't it?
Your old friend,faithful and trustworthy
who never thought  of betraying you
until I turned him into  your most dangerous enemy.
(laughing)
Poor, poor Ken.
You've lost your woman.
You've lost your friend,
and now you'll lose your life.
For I am the true Fist of the North Star.
(loud grunting)
(screaming)
(rumbling)
(grunting)
- You don't seem to understand that you're a dead man.
(loud grunting)
(groaning)
(screaming)
Julia, where is she?
- She's with Shin  at his fortress
just below the southern front.
Oh, help.
- Help, you dareask me for help.
I never realized what an idiot you really are, Jagi.
- You're the idiot.
You've lost everything,you fool, everything.
Yes, admit it you've lost and I've won.
I'm the Fist of the North Star.
You're nothing, nothing.
Do you hear?
(laughing)
Just ask anyone  they'll tell you.
Lord Jagi is the one who (grunting).
- Jagi, damn.
What a waste.
(screaming)
(breathing heavily)
- It's me, your brother Rei.
You all right?
- I recognize your voice.
Oh, yes, I know you're my new master.
What is your will, my lord?
Tell me how may I please you.
- No.
Oh, no.
(water splashing)
(gasping)
Alei.
Ken, is she going  to be all right?
Will she ever know who I am?
- Her memory will return,
but there's nothing I  can do for her blindness.
Her eyes haven't been injured.
She just won't allow herself to see.
Oh, Julia.
(eerie ambient music)
Julia.
- Well, hello.
- Hello yourself.
- Ken, look.
(soft orchestral music)
- Lynn, that's one of Julia's flowers.
- Uh-huh.
- Yes, I remember I was going to be married, wasn't I?
- That's right, Alei.
Go on what else can you recall.
- I had a brother.
His name was Rei, I think.
- Rei is me.
Alei don't you know me?
Come on look at me.
- No, if I look at you, you'll look at me
and you'll see all the  horrible things I've done.
(soft sobbing)
- Alei.
I don't know how to help her.
She says she can't  open her eyes.
- [Alei] Too much pain,too much suffering.
- I know what you mean.
The world's a pretty ugly place right now,
and what's left isn't worth seeing.
- Death everywhere I can't  look at anymore death.
- Feeling sorry for yourself
isn't gonna make  things grow again.
It's gonna take a  lot of hard work.
- Lynn.
- When a bear is fast  asleep in the winter time,
it may look like he's dead, but he's not.
When spring comes, he wakes up full of life,
and the Earth can too if we allwork together to wake it up.
Just reach out and I'll prove it to you.
- All right.
It's a flower and it's blooming.
It's a real flower.
I never thought I'd see a flower again.
- Alei, if you wanna see it,
you gotta open your eyes.
(soft orchestral music)
(gasping)
- [Alei] It'sbeautiful, so beautiful.
(soft sobbing)
(wind blowing swiftly)
(gentle orchestral music)
(footsteps approaching)
- Julia, so beautiful as always.
Why, why do you refuse to accept my gifts
when other women would sell their souls to possess them?
- Just as you would do anything to possess me
if only I were willing to allow it.
You say that you love me
even though you know I feel nothing for you.
Must both our lives be wasted needless and unhappy.
- Given time people can  change, even you someday.
You talk about your life being wasted,
but you're the one  who's wasting it.
You're in love with a ghost, a phantom.
Ken is dead and all your tears and prayers
and hope won't bring him back.
- Liar, if Ken were dead I'd know it.
The Earth is dying.
It must be brought back to life.
- Bring the Earth back to life
why try it's a waste of time, impossible.
Listen, Julia, this town is one of the few places left.
You can eat what you grow.
It's the only place for  thousands of miles around
where the soil is fertile  enough to grow crops
and the water is pure enough to drink.
The poison winds which wind around the world
pass over the graveyards that were once called cities
and then move on to contaminatethe rest of the Earth.
Unless nature can heal her own wounds,
there's no way to stop it.
Eventually, it will all be gone.
The plants, the animals, the people
the cities, not a trace of life,
nothing but a dead and barren ball of rock
spinning through space.
Julia, when there is no future,
we must take what we canbefore it's too late.
- [Rei] This girl you've been looking for, what's her name?
- Julia.
- Julia, she has a lovely name.
- We had planned to get married
and spent the rest of our lives together
spreading the seeds of life
wherever they grow to make  the Earth green again.
I love her, Rei, and youcan't imagine how much.
- I believe that your separation from Julia
must be linked to the ultimate fulfillment of your destiny.
Fate's plan in which wemust all play a part.
I have a hunch that yourroles an important one.
(groaning)
I wouldn't be surprisedif the world needs you
even more than you need Julia.
- Whatever I was destined  to do in this world
will have to waituntil I get Julia back.
Right now that's  all that matters.
- I have no idea what  fate has in store for you,
but you must remainopen to any possibility.
(dramatic orchestral music)
- Listen, give up while you still can
or every one you men  shall die, I promise you.
Raoh, you call yourselfRaoh the Conquerer
and King of the World.
Call yourself Emperor ofthe Galaxy if you like,
but you'll never defeat me or possess an acre of my land.
If you try, you and your entire army will be destroyed.
- Sir, forward.
(loud grunting)
- Destroy them.
(tense orchestral music)
(men grunting)
Now they die.
(grunting)
I've turned my body to steel.
Now I'll crush Raoh's troops as if they were insects
and send Raoh to burn in hell.
(grunting)
(chuckling)
Do they really think they can hurt me
with those pretty little swords of air.
(grunting)
(chuckling)Come now, Raoh.
Is that the best you can do?
- Attack.
(men grunting)
(soft chuckling)
(screaming)
(laughing)
- Why sacrifice more of your men, Raoh,
or are you afraid to face me yourself?
I promise not to hurt  your pretty little horse.
(laughing)
- You fool.
The king doesn't dirty his  hands fighting with scum.
- So I'm scum, am I?
Die, pig.
You think breaking my sword's gonna scare me away.
Guess again, Raoh.
(grunting)
(groaning)
I don't know what  you hit me with,
ah, but it won'tdo you any good.
You're still gonna die.
Hey, why you waving yourhand around like that?
You think I believe in magic or something.
Just what kind of fool do you take me for.
(dramatic orchestral music)
(screaming)
(groaning)
Now you really made me mad, asshole.
(loud screaming)
(screaming)
- Wait and go round up the others,
and destroy them as quickly as possible.
We leave at first light.
(soft music)
- [Shin] I must leave, Julia.
I'm not sure for how long.
Raoh's a madman trying to provethat he's king of the world.
His army's are ravagingwhat's little is left,
and I have to stop him.
- I wish you luck, naturally.
- How incredibly  touching, my love.
Rarely have I heard suchheartfelt sentiment.
- Sir, excuse me, sir
but Raoh and his forces are approaching the out perimeter.
- Already, he is movingfaster than I expected,
but I'm ready for him.
- Sir, one more thing.
We've learned that  Jagi the Pretender
was killed a couple of days ago.
- Hmm?
- His brother Ken, the real Fist of the North Star
is the one that said to have killed him.
(dramatic tone)
- He's alive.
(gentle orchestral music)
When I thought Ken was dead, my heart turned to ice,
and I've been a walking corpse ever since, but no longer.
Ken is alive.
I've got to find  him, I've got to.
(soft grunting)
(grunting)
- Where is Julia?
Search the palace  till she's found.
- Yes, stay on guard and keep alert.
- Captain, have you seen Julia?
- I'm sorry, sir, there's no time to look for her now.
The outer perimeter's been breached.
- No time for Julia, is that right?
- No, sir, I didn't mean that.
I was merely trying to (groaning).
- No time.
Lieutenant, take 100 men off guard duty.
- [Man] Sir.
- Bring Julia to me as soon as you find her.
(dramatic orchestral music)
(gasping)
(grunting)
- Raoh, he's close,
very close, I can feel him.
Welcome.
You kill me.
I kill you.
We destroy each other, what does it matter.
Let it begin.
Raoh, I presume.
- It's all mine and your woman too.
- Huh?
(soft chuckling)
- You came a long way just  to steal a woman, Raoh.
I recall reading something  about ancient Greeks
who did that once, but Inever finished the book.
Let's get on with it.
- All right, if you're that eager to die, I'll oblige you.
Anytime you're ready.
- Your move.
(wind blowing swiftly)
(gentle orchestral music)
- Shin's fortress  is on fire, Julia.
(tense orchestral music)
(footsteps approaching)
(gentle orchestral music)
Shin.
- Hello, Ken.
How nice to see you again.
How have you been?
- [Ken] I've been better.
Where's Julia?
- She's not here right now.
Would you like to  leave a message?
- Very funny.
Afraid I'm not in the mood
for your twisted sense of humor.
Now where is she?
- I thought you'd  ask that question.
I wish I knew, Ken, honestly I do.
- [Ken] Answer me dammit.
- But then we wouldn't fight,
and we're destined to do that.
(dramatic orchestral music)
If I'd known you'd  improved so much,
I would have trained for this fight.
- I don't wanna hurt you, Shin,
but you've left no choice (screaming).
- Well, done, Ken, well done.
(grunting)
- Now tell me, where is she?
- As usual you're a little bit late, Ken.
(spitting)
I couldn't make her happy, Ken no matter how hard I tried.
She could've had it all, you know, anything she wanted.
I gave her everything  and got nothing in return
not a spark not a glimmer
because you were there standing in my way.
- Shin, where is she?
Tell me.
(somber orchestral music)  (grunting)
- This was to be Julia's wedding dress.
It took 10 seamstressesa year to make it.
But of course she'll never wearit now that she's gone away.
- She's gone.
- Oh, yes, far, far away with Raoh.
- Where, Shin?
- Oh, you should've seen them, Ken.
Raoh the Conquerer, a brother you could be proud of
if he weren't such a monster.
- Where have they gone?
- Well, hey, our love has gone away.
Out of the light
(grunting)
into the darkness.
- Out of the light, what do you mean?
- The dungeons of  Cassandra are the
deepest pits of darkness in the world.
- Cassandra, why would he take her there?
- He's built a fortress over the ruins of the old city.
They say its impregnable,
and the dungeon's escape proof.
If only I could have made her love me for an instant.
(loud grunting)
- Shin.
(somber orchestral music)
- To die by your hand only one who loves her as much as--
- [Ken] You loved her even  more than I did, Shin.
No one can love or hate with more passion than a madman.
- [Crowd] King Raoh.
King Raoh.
- Louder, you ungrateful wretches.
I cannot hear you.
Let the king know how much you appreciate all he's done.
You're supposed to say it
along with everyone else, understand?
- [Crowd] Raoh.
King Raoh.
- [Man] Now let's hear it.
- [Crowd] King Raoh.
King Raoh.
- Raoh the Conqueror, pretty impressive.
- Hot damn, I want  a closer look.
- Wait, I wanna go too.
- Don't go far,
and be careful out there.
- Hey.
I can't see a thing from here.
- Wow, far out.
- [Crowd] King Raoh.
- [Man] Hey.
- Oh.
- [Crowd] King Raoh.
King Raoh.
- That presence, who is it?
- [Crowd] King Raoh.
King Raoh.
(high pitch tone ringing)
(gasping)
(horse braying)
- [Crowd] King Raoh.
King Raoh.
- You don't scare me, nah.
- [Crowd] King Raoh.
King Raoh.
- That's Julia, it's got be her,
but what's she doing here?
- [Crowd] King Raoh.
King Raoh.
(rumbling)
- So now they call me Raoh  the Conqueror, why not?
Every one of my enemieshas been annihilated,
all but one, the most dangerous,
the one I wish most to destroy.
But the woman will bring him,
and then he shall die like  all the others before him.
(whooshing)
- That was Julia, are you sure?
- [Rei] From the way Ken described her
it had to be, I'm sure of it.
- Lynn, it couldn't have been.
She's with Shin.
- I'm telling ya there'sno doubt about it.
I don't know why  she's not be Shin
or what she's doing here  but it was her all right.
- Listen, Bat, if Lynn'scertain Julia's here
then we have to take her word for it.
- Yep, she's never wrongabout things like that.
Well, come on then, let's fly.
We'll pay her a visit.
- That palace is huge.
How will we find her?
Look it's obviousshe's a prisoner, right
and prisoners are kept in the dungeon.
- Uh-huh.
- And if there's  one thing I know,
it's that every dungeonhas a secret entrance
that someone like  me can get into.
I'm right, right?
The first thing we gotta do is figure out
the source of the water supply.
It must come from underground, that's obvious.
That's the only way the  factories in the old city
would've had enough water pressure to run all the machinery.
Now if we look at the regional topography
as well as local geological--
It would be safer if you stayed here.
Besides we're not certain you saw her.
It could have been  somebody else.
- I already know it's Julia, and she's awfully sad.
That's why I'm bringingher this flower, Bat.
She needs some cheering up.
(soft grunting)
(grunting)
- We've got a problem.
That door is rusted shut.
It won't budge an inch.
- [Lynn] Never mind, I got it.
- All right, Lynn, way to go.
- Julia.
(soft orchestral music)
- Oh, is it real?
Where did it come from?
- From you, sort of.
- Me?
- [Lynn] You see, I grew it from the seed you gave to Ken,
and he gave to me.
- Incredible, it's  lovely, so lovely.
- Don't you worry.
Ken's gonna get you outof here, I know he will.
- No, you must tell himnot to come near here.
- What do you mean?
- If he comes here he'll die.
Don't you understand?
It's exactly what Raoh wants him to do.
I'm the bait in his trap,
and if Ken comes here Raoh will kill him.
- [Bat] But Julia Ken has no reason to be afraid of Raoh.
He's just a--
(footsteps approaching)
- You must go and quickly.
- We'll find away.
- Let's go.
- We've got to.
(footsteps approaching)
(dramatic orchestral music)
- Who's it from?
Tell me.
Without light it will diequickly as all living things do.
But the one who brought it
will die slowly, very slowly indeed.
(dramatic orchestral music)
- Behold this flower.
(people gasping)
- My, god I can see a living flower.
- No way it couldn't be a  flower, there'll all dead.
- There are no flowers allowed in Lord Raoh's kingdom.
A crime has been committed.
The criminal will come forward,
or this woman will die.
- No, I won't let them hurt her.
- Don't worry she won't be hurt.
Raoh, I'm the one you're looking for.
I take full responsibility.
Add to my list of crimes my friendship
with the one called Fist of the North Star
and with the woman named Julia.
- Well, imagine that, I'm impressed.
- I grew that flower for Julia
from the seeds which shegave me along time ago.
- Flowers inspire hope and hope is unhealthy.
You fool, Uygle.
- Sir, hey you, stay where you are.
By committing this crime you've displeased King Raoh
and must be punished accordingly.
- I'm not here to waste my timefighting with an underling.
My fight is with Raoh the  Conquerer and no one else.
- You upstart (grunting).
(soft chuckling)
Uh, what the hell?
- Raoh, your man's skill with the lash
leaves much to be desired.
Give me someone worthy to fight.
- You miserable mound of dung (chuckling).
- You think you can take me then come on.
(grunting)
- I'll slice you into dog meat.
- All right, Raoh, now it's your turn.
(grunting)
- We're not through yet.
(screaming)
- Well, seems I'm going to haveto fight you after all, Rei.
One can't fight one's destiny.
- Rei, no.
(dramatic tone)
- Lynn, take care of yourself.
There's a whole world depending on you.
Now you, you've gotta die beforeyou can do anymore damage.
- No, Rei, I don't think that my time has come quite yet.
I still have a great many  things do before I die.
In fact, killing you is one of them.
- Then get off your horse, Raoh.
I'm ready, are you?
- Yes, but I see no reason to dismount.
I believe I have a distinct advantage the way things are.
- Quit stalling, Raoh, come on.
- Death shouldn't be rushed.
One should saver  it like fine wine
and enjoy its aroma.
But if in consider of your impatience,
I must kill you now, so be it.
- Enough talk.
Defend yourself, Raoh.
(screaming)
(\"Heart Of Madness\")
(singing in foreign language)
♪ Long, long time
♪ On my way
(singing in foreign language)
♪ Ah, ah standing inthe heart of darkness ♪
♪ Ah, ah give me my  life, give me my energy ♪
♪ Ah, ah fighting inthe heart of darkness ♪
♪ Ah, ah ease my pain, ease my loneliness ♪
♪ Ah, ah standing inthe heart of darkness ♪
♪ Ah, ah give me my  life, give me my energy ♪
♪ Ah, ah fighting inthe heart of darkness ♪
♪ Ah, ah, ease my pain,ease my loneliness ♪
♪ Ah, ah standing inthe heart of darkness ♪
♪ Ah, ah give me my  life, give me my energy ♪
♪ Ah, ah fighting inthe heart of darkness ♪
♪ Ah, ah ease my pain, ease my loneliness ♪
♪ Whoa, whoa
- Ken.
(high pitch tone ringing)
Ken, hurry.
(gasping)
- Rei, you smell it?
That's the smell of death.
(grunting)
- No.
(groaning)
- Ken.
- Julia.
(soft chuckling)
- So you've come.
- Let him go, Raoh, he's dying.
(somber orchestral music)
You bastard.
- My goodness I'm  surprised at you.
Is that any way to talkto your older brother?
You must learn to show me more respect.
See, it's different now.
I'm a king,
and a king must demand respect from everyone.
- Ken.
Ken, fight 'em and  you both will die.
You'll kill each other until what end.
You're too important to the next stage
of man's history to throw your life away.
(groaning)
Please, Ken, think  of the children,
the innocent yet unborn,
and think of the ones you love
and who love you anddepend on your strength.
They too have a role to play in the new era of man.
Will they be able to survive
without you to protect them?
And Julia, what if Julia,
she needs you so much.
Please, Ken, don't fight Raoh.
(soft groaning)
- Rei.
- Raoh the Conquerer, your time has come.
(dramatic orchestral music)
(laughing)
- Well, now let's see whatyou're made of, little brother.
(chuckling)
Come now, little brother.
After all, this time you must
be able to do better than that.
Even your little slut, Julia,
put up more of afight than this.
So did Ryuuken, our dear departed father.
He's dead, Ken, I killed him.
(tense orchestral music)
And now the final contest is at hand.
(horse braying)
Whoa.
Now I can see it.
Ken's aura is strong, very strong.
Come, little brother.
Having strength is one thing
but knowing how to  use it is another.
(crowd gasping)
(crowd screaming)
(gasping)
- Ken.
(Julia screaming)
- [Kids] Julia.
- Look.
(loud grunting)
(grunting)
(gasping)
(screaming)
- You're better, much better.
I had no idea how  far you'd come.
You're a very good fighter, exceptional in fact.
But you're no matchfor me, little brother,
and never will be.
(loud grunting)
(tense music)
(screaming)
(grunting)
I hope for your sake that the
hereafter is a better world than this.
(groaning)
Let's finish it now (groaning).
(loud groaning)
(grunting)
(groaning)
(screaming)
Come then.
(loud groaning)
(grunting)
(breathing heavily)
Now die damn you, die!
- No, don't!
(soft orchestral music)
Please wait.
I've got to talk to you.
It's important.
Very well, what do you want?
To stop you from killing him.
To stop all this killing.
- Those who betray thefirst of the north star
deserve to die.
- [Man] Power without perceptionis spiritually useless
and therefore of no true value.
- Ryuken.
You ask me to spare Ken's life, so be it.
Fate has entrusted him with a unique responsibility
The protection of someone on who the earth's future depends
Someone special.
You.
You have a responsibility, too.
He'll need looking after for a while, you needn't worry,
With his strength and alittle care his wounds
will heal before long.
(groaning)
If Ken wants to find me,
tell him I'll be at Ryuken's grave, paying my respects.
(bright orchestral music)
- [Bat] I wonder what happened to Ken.
- And Julia, I'm sure he'll find her.
He'll come back some day  and Julia will be with him
'cause I know he won't stop searching till he finds her.
Oh, look!
- Huh?
(grand orchestral music)
- [Bat] Are those what I think they are?
- Yes!
Flowers!
They're growing again.
- Have you ever seen anything so wonderful?
(children giggling)
(wind howling)
(dramatic synth music)
- Julia.