[HANSEN]
Well, isn't that something.
[TOADY 11A] She was wanderin'
around all by herself
in the western seas.
[HANSEN]
Hell of a job, men.
This is a merfolk child.
She'll bring in a
hefty price, for sure.
Now, let's get ready
for the auction.
[TOADIES]
Yes, sir!
Mama.
[WILL]
Please forgive me, Ilwer!
I've been such a burden to you.
Don't be ridiculous!
I'm glad you're home safe.
To be honest, I didn't
think you'd make it back alive.
Eh. He just got
lucky, that's all.
Anyway. I'm gonna need one
more status plate, please,
if you don't mind.
[ILWER]
You got it.
[TIO] I'm sorry, but are you
sure it was appropriate for me
to receive a gold
top‐rank status plate?
[YUE]
Sure.
Oh! I forgot.
You made a promise, Hajime!
Hey, don't be mean!
You said that if I
worked really hard,
you would show me around
to all the touristy places
in Fuhren, remember?
Hm? What's the matter?
[TIO] I heard this city
was a hub for commerce,
but it seems there's more
to it than meets the eye.
Well, I don't care
who comes after us.
I'll take 'em down
in a heartbeat.
You honestly don't
care who they are?
[HAJIME]
Nope.
It could be a god
for all I care.
[TIO whimpering]
We have only one enemy.
God himself.
He's wise and strong, but still,
he's by no means indestructible.
[groans]
Someday, the time will come...
...when he must cease
his dark machinations.
One day, child,
a mighty being will appear
who possesses the ability
to defeat God.
So, Tio.
Yes, Father?
You must live.
[TIO crying]
[ELDER 11A]
Tio! You did come!
[TIO]
Indeed, Elder.
I felt a strange
thrumming in my chest.
Is there trouble here
on the continent?
Yes, it looks as though
God has summoned forth
a host of alien beings, and
their numbers are quite great.
Then I shall go at once.
[DRAGONPEOPLE gasp]
I have no choice.
This will change
our world immensely.
Something deep inside
is telling me it's true.
Esteemed leader,
and my beloved
dragon brethren, as well!
I have no way of predicting
what destiny awaits me,
nor what anyone's fate holds.
But... I feel that
things will change.
And that feeling...
...is really, really good!
[slap]
[TIO whimpering]
Hurry and wake up.
It's shopping time!
[TIO yelps]
This kind of weather
is perfect for a date!
Watch where you're
going, or you'll trip.
[SHEA chuckles]
Hey, Hajime, look at that!
Can we go there next?
[HAJIME]
Hm? An aquarium?
[SHEA]
Ah!
Wow. So this is a monster
that can talk, huh?
Says its name is Lehman.
Hey, pal.
Can you actually talk, or what?
Introductions first.
I don't know you.
My name's Hajime.
Tell me, Lehman.
Just what the hell are you?
[LEHMAN]
Don't be rude.
If I asked you what a human was,
how would you answer that, huh?
Fine.
If I have to give
an answer, I'm just me.
Nothing more than that,
and nothing less.
Now I have a question.
How exactly are you able
to detect the presence
of monsters nearby?
[HAJIME] If I had to guess,
I'd say it's 'cause I've
eaten monsters.
[LEHMAN]
Hmm?
[GIRL 11A]
Aw, that one's adorable!
[GUY 11A]
Not as adorable as you, darling.
[GIRL 11A]
You're so sweet!
[GUY 11A]
No, you!
[LEHMAN sobs]
You're making me cry!
To think, you were desperate
enough to eat monsters!
And despite all that, you turned
out to be such a decent fellow!
[SHEA]
Hey. No fair.
We're supposed to be on a date,
but you're still talking
to this crusty old monster.
Oh, no!
I'm spoiling your date?
I'm sorry about that, chum.
It's fine.
We should get
going soon, though.
Let me ask you
one more thing first:
what are you doing
in this aquarium?
Well... I had set off
alone on a journey,
but then I ended up swimming
into an underground current,
which brought me to the
surface, and here we are.
[HAJIME, SHEA gasp]
[LEHMAN]
What's wrong?
[HAJIME]
Uh... Lehman?
I'm just spitballing here,
but would you like us
to get you out?
Thanks, buddy. Really!
Uh... Don't mention it.
We're friends!
[BOTH laugh]
[LEHMAN]
You know...
When I was brought
to that prison,
there was a little
merfolk girl around, too.
Poor thing.
Seemed like she was being
bought and sold, just like me.
I should warn you,
there's a huge gang of slavers
in this city.
Better watch your back,
especially you, pretty lady.
[SHEA] Don't worry,
I'll be extra careful!
You do the same, okay?
[LEHMAN]
Thank you! Farewell!
Yue. Are you really
all right with this?
Him and Shea?
What else?
I mean, those two seem to be
growing awfully close recently,
don't you think?
[YUE]
That's wonderful.
[TIO]
What did you say?
You would honestly be
pleased to see another woman
with the man that you love?
[YUE]
She's not just anyone.
She's Shea.
[TIO]
Hmm?
You're chowing down.
Is it really that good?
Yes! Oh, question!
I just want to make sure.
You are okay with Tio
joining us, right?
Joining us, huh?
More like taking
advantage of the confusion
and then tagging along.
[SHEA chuckles]
You don't like her?
Well, putting aside the fact
that she's a raging pervert,
I don't mind her. And you?
Oh, I like Tio! Pervert or not!
Is there something wrong?
[HAJIME]
Not sure.
It's just, my Sense Presence
caught onto someone nearby.
Well, yeah, look around.
We're surrounded by people.
No, this is coming from below.
[SHEA]
Below?
The sewers, you mean?
And whoever it is,
they're small and weak.
Must be a kid.
Huh?
[SHOPKEEP 11A]
Here's your change.
Thanks so much.
At first, she was always
hanging on Hajime.
And her motives were
so blatantly obvious
that it was annoying.
But then I saw...
‐‐Something else?
‐‐Mm‐hmm.
She fights for the things
she loves, and people too.
She gives it
everything she's got.
That's so admirable.
She faces the world head‐on.
It's true that she
likes Hajime quite a bit.
However, she likes me, too.
Not in the same way,
but the exact same amount.
[chuckles]
Isn't that precious?
Poor girl! Is she...?
She's still breathing.
[HANSEN]
What?! She got away?!
[TOADY 11A]
I'm sorry! [grunts]
Do you know how much
money that girl's worth?
Go find her!
[TOADIES]
Yes, sir!
[door opens, closes]
[SHEA]
She's one of the merfolk.
They live all the way
out in the western seas.
So it's strange to see one here.
And because they
benefit the kingdom,
they're the only race of
beastmen that are protected.
Obviously she's here because
something bad happened.
Hey!
[stomach growls]
Hey, there. Got a name?
Myu.
[HAJIME]
Myu, huh?
I'm Hajime, and this is Shea.
[MYU]
Ah...!
[MYU, SHEA laugh]
[SHEA]
Here.
Tastes good, right?
‐‐[MYU] Mm‐hmm.
‐‐[door opens]
[HAJIME]
Hey, I'm back.
As tough as you are,
you're pretty good at playing
caretaker, too.
I'm just drying her hair.
[SHEA chuckles]
[HAJIME] Let's talk about
where to go from here.
Maybe we should find
out Myu's story.
[HAJIME]
Good call.
Here you are. Enjoy.
[TIO] I see, so all three of you
have formed a close bond,
each bringing something
different to the relationship.
Still. You must be
at least a trifle worried.
[YUE]
Hm?
[TIO] What if she steals
Master's heart away?
She's a charming girl,
and he clearly cares for her.
Yes, he does.
I want him to be surrounded
by people he cares about.
But...
I'm special to Hajime.
If she tries to steal him,
then she will fail.
And so will you.
[TIO]
Please!
I have no desire
to challenge you.
So long as he continues
his rough treatment of me,
I'll be content.
Pervert.
[TIO laughing]
[SHEA]
Poor thing.
You got separated
from your mother?
[MYU]
Mm‐hmm.
[HAJIME] Must be that
gang of slavers Lehman
was talking about.
They were probably
planning to sell her off
at some kind of
black‐market auction.
Who would do
something like that?
[HAJIME]
A real shithead, that's who.
And it's starting to sound
like this city is full of 'em.
[SHEA]
So what do we do with her?
She's all alone.
[HAJIME] Our best bet's
gonna be to leave her
with the city guard.
Dealing with lost kids probably
falls under their purview.
But...
You said the merfolk
were protected.
I'm sure they'll take
good care of her.
Understand, Myu?
We're gonna take you
to some nice people
who will keep you safe.
They'll look after you and
make sure you get back home
where you belong.
But Big Brother...
Trust me.
It'll be better this way.
No!
[HAJIME]
Hey, now, you'll be fine.
[MYU]
Please don't do this!
I wanna stay with you!
[MYU crying]
[GUARD 11A chuckles]
[crying continues]
[MYU]
Big Brother...
Are you leaving
because you hate me?
[crying continues]
[explosion]
[CROWD gasping, chattering]
[HAJIME gasps]
You see that smoke?
[SHEA gasps]
[SHEA]
Over here!
[HAJIME] "If you don't
want the merkid to die,
bring us the bunny girl.
Otherwise, her death
is on your hands."
Oh, no! I've gotta find her!
[HAJIME]
I'm coming with you.
These fools are my enemies now.
What a lovely day this has been.
[chuckles]
[TOADY 11B yells]
[CROWD gasping]
[HAJIME] I thought I sensed
a familiar presence.
[SHEA] Are my eyes
playing tricks on me?
What are you two doing here?
[YUE]
I could ask you the same thing.
Isn't this a bit much
for a date?
[TIO] Master, have you been
embroiled in some sort of
thrilling debauchery?
We saved a little merfolk girl
from a bunch of slave traders,
but they took her back again.
Meaning they've sentenced
themselves to death.
Where's the girl now?
That's a good question
no one wants to answer.
We tried torture, but we
still haven't come up with
any solid leads.
So we figured the best
thing we could do would be
to make an example out
of all the gangs involved
in this awful child
trafficking business.
We could use your help.
He's discovered something
else he finds important.
[HAJIME]
Huh?
[TIO] If you wish for aid,
master, I can't deny you.
What she said.
Good.
We'll break into two groups
and search for her.
Yue's with me.
Let's be quick about this.
[HANSEN]
Where the hell are they?!
[TOADY 11C]
Boss!
[blasts]
[SHEA yelling]
What's going on?
‐‐Go check it out, right now!
‐‐Yes, sir!
[SHEA]
Oh, I'm sorry, did we interrupt?
You guys make me sick.
A trade that victimizes
innocent children.
I must admit,
I'm quite perturbed.
[TIO]
Hell is too good for you!
[TOADIES yell]
[SLAVERS]
Ooh...
[MYU] Are you leaving
because you hate me?
[MYU gasps]
Dammit! Don't just sit there.
Cry! Scream!
Put on a show for us!
Soon enough you'll learn
how a good girl acts.
You give me any trouble
and you're dead.
[HAJIME]
That's funny.
I was about to say the same
thing to you, asshole.
[HANSEN]
Who's there?!
[grunts]
Bastard!
[SLAVERS yelling]
[HAJIME]
Hey, Myu.
Aw, man.
Looks like we're gonna
have to dry you off again.
Big brother!
[crying]
Hold on. Close your
eyes for a second.
Uh, okay.
[HAJIME]
You can open them now.
Amazing! How are we flying?
Well, it's not
technically flying.
Anyway...
You're about to see one
heck of a fireworks display.
What's that?
Trust me, you'll like 'em.
Just say "Boom!"
when you're ready.
Okay, boom!
Pretty impressive, huh?
What do you think, Myu?
They're kinda scary.
[gasps]
Something's in the smoke!
Mm‐hmm. We've got some
bad guys to deal with.
[HAJIME]
I'd like for you to meet Yue.
She's my lover.
[MYU]
Huh?
No fair. You're just so cute!
Plus... You have been
very brave today.
You should be proud.
[MYU crying]
What's going on?
Wait, don't tell me.
I bet you said
something mean to Myu.
[HAJIME]
I don't bully little girls.
Feel free to take your
frustrations out on me.
[HAJIME]
Shut it, masochist.
[TIO]
Ooh!
[HAJIME]
Oh, yeah, that's our pervert.
Her name's Tio. Ignore her.
Big Brother.
Thank you for saving me!
Yeah, sure.
But hey...
How about we drop this whole
big brother thing now?
My name's Hajime.
[MYU]
How 'bout "Papa"?
No. That's worse.
Hajime will do just fine.
Unless it translates
to "Papa" in merfolk?
Papa's just Papa.
[YUE]
Why would you call him that?
Well, because.
I don't have a Papa.
But I can promote
my big brother!
Uh, this is all making
me very uncomfortable.
I know I have white hair,
but I'm still 17.
'Kay. What about "dad"?
[HAJIME] On second thought,
Big Brother works.
Let's go with that.
Just stop implying
I'm your father.
No! Don't be
so mean to me, Papa!
Hajime. I want a baby.
Ooh, yes, me too, please!
[TIO]
Cruel Master.
I, too, am prepared to conceive.
Let's not stall the
procreation any longer‐‐
[HAJIME] The only thing
that's stalled is your brain.
[TIO] Why am I the only
one you're admonishing?
[ENDO]
ARIFURETA:
From Commonplace
to World's Strongest.