Ya‐hoo! This rules!
There she goes.
She's as loud as ever,
but at least she's out there
instead of in here.
[SHEA]
Butt up!
And it's Rabbit time!
Vroom, vroom! Vroom!
[HAJIME growls]
Ramming time!
[SHEA laughing]
Papa! That looks fun,
I wanna try.
There's no way I'm
lettin' you do that!
Aww!
Myu, listen to Papa.
Boo.
I can teach you
how to ride it later.
But, for now, sit tight, okay?
[HAJIME gasps]
It may seem like
he's being mean,
but he's worried
for your safety.
Such unexpected tenderness.
I can't contain my excitement!
Oh! Ohh!
Big Sister Yue.
Big Sister Tio is
breathing heavy again.
Yes, she's very sick.
And there's no cure.
[SHEA]
Ya‐hoo! Vroom!
Papa? Is something wrong?
No. I'm fine.
I was just thinking
about the past.
It's only been four months, but
it feels like years have passed.
[HAJIME]
You the guild leader?
[LOA]
Hm? Yes, indeed, I am.
The name is Loa Bawavis.
Here, we've got a letter for
you from the adventurer's
guild leader over in Fuhren.
[LOA]
Thank you.
Huh. It seems to be an
introduction of sorts.
Mmm. It sounds like you folks
went on quite a rampage.
[HAJIME] There was some
structural damage.
[LOA] Hard to believe I've
never heard of a group capable
of destroying an army of 60,000
and devastating an entire
criminal underground until now.
But I've never known Ilwer
to lie on another's behalf.
[ENDO panting]
Urgent message! There's
a demon in the labyrinth!
And just who the hell are you?
Huh...
[LOA]
Nagumo. Do you know this man?
Wait. Nagumo?
Is that really you?
[HAJIME] You still gotta burst
into a room to be noticed,
eh, Endo?
Well, it would seem
you two know each other.
But I still don't know you.
Wait, weren't you with the hero
party that came through earlier?
I... I'm Endo.
Uh... are...
Are you really Nagumo?
I'm sorry.
You seem different is all.
Like, your appearance and stuff.
Yeah, well, I clawed my way
up from the pits of hell.
So of course I changed a bit.
Changed a bit?
More like a lot.
But you're really here.
You're alive.
I can't believe it.
[gasps]
Wait. Are you telling me
you were strong enough
to get through the
whole labyrinth alone?
[HAJIME]
Pretty much.
Then you have to help me!
We need to go to
the labyrinth, now!
They're all gonna
die down there!
Huh?
[ENDO]
Everyone is going to die!
[GROUP gasps]
[SHIZUKU]
Something's not right.
[KOUKI]
We've explored so much.
So why haven't we
encountered any monsters yet?
Maybe it's the floor we're on.
It could just be that there're
no monsters down here.
Kouki. I think we
should head back.
Why's that?
I've got a bad feeling
about this place.
We ought to consult Captain
Meld before moving forward.
[KOUKI]
I understand, but...
Hey, guys?
This is monster blood, isn't it?
[SHIZUKU] There's not
a lot of light down here,
so it's hard
to tell for sure.
[HIYAMA]
There's a ton of it!
[ENDO]
And it looks fresh.
Be on your guard.
Whatever monster
did this is strong.
You think that a monster
attacked another monster?
[ENDO] Not only that,
but it's hidden its tracks.
[KOUKI] If there are
only tracks in this area,
that means it didn't have
time to cover them up.
That, or...
[DEMON 12A]
It's a trap.
[footsteps]
[KOUKI]
A demon?
[DEMON 12A] You, there, in the
ridiculously shiny white armor.
You're a hero, aren't you?
Have you ever considered
changing sides?
What? Change sides?
What are you saying?
I'm asking you to join us.
Never!
[DEMON 12A] Your friends
are welcome to come too,
if they'd like.
My answer isn't changing.
[DEMON 12A]
What a shame.
It never hurts to ask, though.
One of your friends has
already said yes, after all.
There's no way that's true.
You won't fool us!
[DEMON 12A]
I wouldn't be so sure.
[GROUP gasps]
[DEMON 12A] I think anyone
would agree I've given you
plenty of chances to cooperate.
The monsters can have you now.
[MONSTER 12A growls]
[SHIZUKU yelling]
[SUZU yelling]
[KOUKI]
Shizuku! Suzu!
[KAORI]
Bathe in protective light.
Turning tide and heavens.
Divine Intervention!
Get away from Shizuku!
[grunts]
I won't let you!
[ERI] Engulf mine enemies,
O crimson mother!
Reckless Blaze!
[RYUTARO yells]
[KOUKI gasps]
[RYUTARO grunts]
What is with these things?
[ERI]
Reckless Blaze!
[RYUTARO]
There're so many of them!
[ENDO]
You guys! Watch out!
[ERI]
No way.
Oh, no!
[SUZU] Let the light of
protection grow tenfold,
restored by my will!
Now, Divine...
...Intervention!
Damn! How the hell are
these monsters so strong?
Hiyama, listen!
I'm going to try to get close.
When I do, I'll need you
to protect the others.
Yeah. Sure, protect
the others, I got it.
[SHIZUKU grunting]
[KOUKI yelling]
[BIRD squawks]
She can heal them?
[ENDO] We've never encountered
anything this strong before.
How do we beat them?
We can't win.
Endo, I need you
to do something.
Are you listening?
Run away.
Go find Captain Meld.
[ENDO]
Huh?
[SHIZUKU] You're our best shot
at getting a message out
without being noticed.
Sneak out of here
and bring back help.
[ENDO]
Me?
[SHIZUKU]
You're the only one who can.
[ENDO]
I'll be back soon, I promise!
I'll be back!
I promise.
[crunch]
Agh! What the hell
is up with this kid?
Papa!
And just what gives you the
right to yell at my daughter
like that? Huh?
I'll freakin' kill you!
[ENDO whimpers]
Well, well.
He's really a papa now.
He didn't even hesitate
to call her his daughter, huh?
He did not. But the true
test of his fatherhood
will be letting her go.
[HAJIME]
Aw, that was scary, huh?
Did he yell at you?
It's okay, baby.
[DEMON 12A]
Mmm?
You're looking tired.
Wanna rethink your answer now?
I'll never give up!
You haven't won this yet!
Limit Break!
O light, make my will
sharp as a blade's edge
and slice through my enemies.
Blinding Edge!
[DEMON 12A] By mine eye,
all that is known to my enemy
shall be shut closed.
And all that will remain is
their cold, impending demise.
Let my enemies be crushed.
Returned to the earth.
Crashing Gaol!
[SHIZUKU gasps]
Taniguchi, we need
protection, now!
Got it!
Enemies of God may not
tread upon his domain.
Hallowed Ground!
[SUZU grunting]
[DEMON 12A chuckles]
[ERI]
Watch out!
Protect Suzu!
[SUZU coughs]
[RYUTARO]
Taniguchi!
[ERI gasps]
Heed me, O wind.
Blustering Blast!
[ERI]
It can't be!
[KAORI]
Suzu, no!
[KOUKI grunts]
[SHIZUKU]
Kouki!
Dammit!
We must retreat!
They killed one of our friends
and we're just gonna run?!
Calm down and think!
[ENDO] I ran to Captain Meld
to tell him about the demon
as quickly as I could.
[panting]
[ENDO] The captain should be
guarding the teleportation
circle to the 70th floor.
[ENDO panting]
It's terrible! You have to help!
Kosuke!
What are you doing up here?
Wait, where are the others?
[ENDO]
The others...
[ENDO crying]
[MELD]
You didn't abandon them, Kosuke.
It would have been impossible
for anyone else to get here.
You've given them a chance.
[ENDO] They've figured out
a way to retreat by now.
So I have to get back
and help them escape.
[ENDO, MELD grunt]
[ENDO]
No way. I was followed?
Quit feeling sorry for
yourself and stand up.
Quick, to the surface!
[ENDO gasps]
[SOLDIER 12A yells]
[SOLDIER 12B grunting]
Don't just sit there.
Go tell the guild leader
what's going on down here.
[ENDO]
But, what about you, Captain?
[MALE SOLDIER 12B grunting]
Destroy the circle when
you reach the other side.
We'll protect it with our lives.
[ENDO]
But...
Tell the people above about
the demon before it's too late!
[MELD yells]
Stand up! Do your duty!
Now witness...
...the strength and resolve of
the Heilich Kingdom Knights!
All I can do is survive.
And send messages.
Pathetic.
[KOUKI panting]
[CREATURE growls]
[RYUTARO grunts]
[SHIZUKU]
Here.
[KOUKI]
Thank you.
You owe me big time.
[growling]
[GROUP panting]
[HIYAMA]
Hey!
Maybe the safest thing for
us is to do what she says
and accept her offer.
[KOUKI]
What the hell are you saying?
[ERI]
Hiyama's right.
I don't see any other way
we get out of this alive.
No, you can't be serious.
I just don't want us to die.
Is that really such a bad thing?
We can't trust that
she'll let us live.
Listen to yourself!
She's been after us
since you said no!
If we keep running,
she'll keep on killing us.
I say it's time that
we try something else!
Even if we can't trust
her offer is genuine,
it's the only chance
that we have.
[MELD]
The most important thing
is that you do whatever
it takes to survive.
[grunting]
[KOUKI]
Captain Meld!
[MELD]
We were selfish.
Asking you children
to fight our war.
‐‐[weapon thrust]
‐‐[grunts]
[grunting]
[GROUP gasps]
I'm sorry.
Captain Meld, no!
[KOUKI growling]
Kouki, you can't!
If you use Limit Break right
now, your body will give out!
[KOUKI growls]
[HAJIME]
A demon, huh?
Listen, Nagumo.
If what Ilwer says
of you is true,
then I have a formal
request I'd like to make.
[HAJIME] I think I've got some
idea of what that might be.
[ENDO]
Nagumo! They're your friends!
You'd do anything to
save your friends, right?
[HAJIME]
They're your friends, not mine.
[ENDO]
Huh?
[HAJIME]
I'll give it to you straight.
As far as I'm concerned,
you guys are strangers.
We're from the same
world, but that's it.
Nothing more.
[ENDO]
What?
[KOUKI yelling]
This is for Captain Meld!
[KOUKI yells]
[DEMON 12A grunts]
[DEMON 12A grunts, coughs]
I'll kill you!
[gasps]
Oh, are you surprised?
I know it can be difficult for
you humans to comprehend.
There's a lot more
to me than the monsters
you're used to killing.
Yeah? So what?
[DEMON 12A] You should
learn more about exploiting
your enemy's weaknesses.
This is a war, after all.
[KOUKI yelling]
Kouki, no!
Nagumo. I beg you.
Help them.
They need you.
I promise I'll protect you.
You'll be safe.
Even if it was, I owe you.
You gave me a chance,
and I am not gonna waste it.
You could've saved him,
but you chose death?
[MYU]
My Papa's strong!
He can save them, no problem!
[SHEA] Are you really sure
you don't want to?
It would be simple for
one such as yourself.
The decision is yours to make.
I'll always follow you,
no matter what.
Fine, let's go.
[KAORI]
I can't do it.
I... don't have enough
mana left to help.
[HORSE FACE 12A growls]
[SHIZUKU grunts]
Look at you.
I didn't think anyone in
your party actually had
the capacity for murder,
but you're really
prepared to kill me.
[SHIZUKU] Kouki's kindhearted
nature held us back.
He wasn't ready
to kill, but I am.
I'll fix his mistake!
[HORSE FACE 12B growls]
[SHIZUKU grunting]
[SHIZUKU coughs]
Shizuku!
[HORSE FACES growling]
[SUZU chuckles]
It looks like I woke
up just in time, huh?
[SHIZUKU coughs]
I'm here now!
[SHIZUKU]
Kaori. You have to go back.
It isn't safe to stay.
[HORSE FACES growl]
[KAORI]
It isn't safe anywhere.
So I...
I would rather be here with you.
I'm glad you are.
[HORSE FACES growling]
[KAORI]
I'm sorry, Nagumo!
It looks like I can't
keep my promise.
[SHIZUKU]
What the hell just happened?
[HAJIME] Kinda nice to see
the two of you are still
getting along.
[KAORI]
Nagumo?
[HAJIME]
ARIFURETA:
From Commonplace
to World's Strongest.