[HAJIME]
So, Shimizu's gone missing?
And we have no idea
where he might be.
I really hope he isn't in
trouble or anything.
Nah, I'm sure he'll be fine.
If you say so.
After all, you survived horrible
odds and came back to us.
Yeah, well.
Don't forget that
I'm not sticking around.
Ms. Aiko?
Oh. Wow.
You're so nice to her.
Well, she has done
a lot for me in the past,
so it's the least I can do.
Huh...
[HAJIME]
Hm? What's wrong?
It's nothing.
But I'm sitting
there on the way back.
You got it.
Wait, you guys, that's no fair.
I wanna be up there next
to you, not stuck in the back
with a bunch of people
I barely even know.
Can't you see
I'm trying to drive, here?
Huh?
[AIKO]
Uh, what are those?
Huh? Human‐seeking
automatons called Ornis.
They use a gravity stone to fly
and an induction stone to think.
Oh, and there's also a
peering stone inside of them
that's connected to my eye,
so I can see what they see.
Huh?
What do we have here?
You already located a clue?
[ALL]
Huh?
[HAJIME]
Looks like a busted shield
and some other gear.
Yeah.
We should go check this out.
Those are tracks.
If I had to guess,
these were made by a
huge, four‐legged creature.
There are stories going around.
They say there's
a monster lurking
beyond these two mountains.
D'you think something
like that made this crater?
Huh? I'm sensing someone's
presence nearby.
Feels like it's human.
Or at least close enough.
If someone's alive out there,
they might need our help!
Over there.
Behind that waterfall.
Yue.
Fissuring Wave.
Go, Wind Wall
Bingo.
[grunts]
[shrieks]
Hey you.
Is your name Will?
Huh? Whoa, you know me?
I mean, yeah.
That's me, Will Cudeta.
All right.
Hajime Nagumo.
The head of the Fuhren
Adventurer's Guild sent me
to rescue you.
[WILL]
No matter how hard we fought,
the monsters
wouldn't stop coming.
Before we knew it,
they had us cornered.
Then it showed up.
Huh?
What did?
[WILL]
The black dragon.
Dragon?
I don't deserve this.
Why should I get to live?
Everyone else in
my party was slaughtered.
I'm alive,
and part of me is glad.
But when I think about what
happened to the others, I just.
Nagu‐‐
Of course you're glad
you didn't get killed.
Why wouldn't you be?
Wanting to live is human.
It's called the
survival instinct,
and we'd all be
screwed without it.
You're totally in
the right to be glad.
I wish they could've...
The only thing you
can do for the people
who died here is keep living on.
Drag your feet forward one
at a time and live on.
Live on.
Just like that?
That's right.
Someday you might find there
was a reason you survived,
but only if you
keep on fighting.
Do you understand?
Well, we've got
what we came for.
Time to head back.
[gasps]
[shrieks]
There it is!
[HAJIME]
The dragon.
[gasps]
Get moving!
Let's go.
Hajime!
This thing is
no ordinary monster.
I've got you.
I'll help you hold
against its fire.
[YUE]
Heavenly Calamity!
One strike from this,
and it's over!
[SHEA gasps]
[SHEA]
Missed me!
Okay, let's try that again!
[yelps]
[screams]
Huh?!
Go! Yue!
Right. I've got this.
[gasps] We have to help them.
Right. I'll do my best.
Ms. Aiko! Round up the others
and don't let them interfere.
But you're still‐‐
[HAJIME]
You're in the way.
Yue! Protect everyone else.
I'll take out the dragon.
Right. I've got it covered.
If you don't want to die,
get behind me now.
I thought we could help,
but we're just holding him back.
[HAJIME]
It seems fixated on Will.
Heh. I'm not used to monsters
ignoring me like this.
I guess I'll just have
to do a better job
of holding its attention, then.
Heh.
What's wrong?
Huh?
That hurt?
[roars]
[HAJIME]
How about that?
Painful, right?
That was awesome.
Shea!
Right! Coming!
[sighs]
This thing sure isn't
going down easily.
[HAJIME] I heard there
were some seriously tough
monsters out here,
but I honestly wasn't expecting
this much of a challenge.
Yue, Shea, you guys ever
heard of the expression
"kick the dragon
in its scaly ass"?
A dragon's only weak point
is where it doesn't have scales.
They say they're
so well‐defended,
when they fall asleep,
almost nothing can wake them.
But if you attack
one particular spot,
it's a different story entirely.
Take it in the ass and die!
[ALL gasp]
[TIO gasps]
[shrieks]
What are you doing?
[sobs] My rear!
My precious behind!
Oh, that stings.
Ouch.
Squirming makes it worse.
Take it out!
I beseech you.
I'll do anything.
So long as you pull it out!
[wails]
Now, then.
You must be one of
the dragonborn, yes?
[TIO]
Indeed!
I'm a member of the
esteemed dragonborn race!
Wild circumstances have
led me to this predicament.
I'll tell you everything.
But only if you remove
this foreign object
from my nether regions!
I think not.
[TIO squeals]
I am begging you!
You've pushed me
to the breaking point.
Plus, I'm almost out of mana,
and if I return to my original
form with this inside of me,
it'd be a disaster.
Why are you on this mountain?
[TIO]
I told you, I'll relay my story.
Just remove his sword
from my sheath.
Imagine what it feels like
to have this maniac ram you‐‐
[wails]
You better answer
Yue's questions.
[TIO]
It's going in deeper!
Don't force it like that!
This is too much.
It feels like
I'm going to rip apart!
[HAJIME] The dragonborn
are supposedly all dead.
So what's one doing out
here attacking adventurers.
Better start talking fast.
[TIO] No, please, twisting
it makes even harder to bear!
I'll spill my secrets.
When you stop
spearing my backside!
[TIO]
I was manipulated.
I was no more than
some horrible villain's tool!
He's the one who told me
to kill that young man
and his companions.
Keep going, ya beast.
[TIO] I left my hidden village
to investigate rumors
that were circulating
about travelers who
came from another world.
But on my journey
to the closest town,
I tired and paused for a rest.
A lovely nap on
a mountain ledge.
Naturally I stayed
in my dragon form,
as there were vicious
monsters in the vicinity.
While I slumbered in peace,
a man dressed in dark robes
somehow stumbled upon
my resting place and
took advantage of me.
He must have used some
sort of mind‐control magic
to steal my freedom and force me
to act out his terrible wishes.
The man was an expert
of his wicked craft.
And since he cast his spell over
the course of an entire day,
it was far too strong to resist!
So you're telling me, that you
were in such a deep sleep,
that this idiot was able to
spend a whole day castin' magic,
and you didn't even
know he was there?
[WILL]
I don't believe you!
You're saying
it's not your fault?
How convenient that someone
else made you kill my friends!
How are we supposed to know
if you're telling us the truth?
I bet you made
that entire story up
just to save your
worthless hide.
[TIO]
I swear, this is what happened.
The dragonborn
are a proud people.
We'd never stoop to falsehoods.
Liar!
[YUE]
What she says is true.
[WILL]
What proof do you have?
[YUE] The dragonborn
are noble and honest.
You heard her.
She put her pride
on the line, right?
That's how I'm sure
she's not lying.
But. Wait!
Besides,
I know what the eyes
of a liar look like,
and hers are pure.
[TIO] To think there
is someone in this age
who understands the way
of the dragonborn.
I am the last surviving vampire.
Three centuries ago,
I was often told to
look to the dragonborn
as models of how
royalty should behave.
[TIO]
Incredible!
We'd received news
in our village
that the vampires
were eradicated.
And, yet, here sits
a princess of their ilk.
Who cares?
It doesn't matter,
you still killed them all!
You can't get away with that!
[TIO] I don't wish to start
some kind of conflict
between our peoples.
That said, it is true that
I did take innocent lives.
But if you order me
to atone for my sins,
then, I will accept
a fitting punishment.
I only ask that you
temporarily postpone it.
Until I can stop that dangerous
man and whatever it is he plots.
Will you give me the chance
to prevent another tragedy?
Nah. You've caused me more
than enough trouble already.
Do you think I give
a damn about what you want?
It's time for you to die.
[TIO]
Seriously?
You would take my life
and let that man
get away with evil deeds,
causing unimaginable
disasters to befall humanity?
What kind of fool are you?
Have you know sense of decency‐‐
You're going to kill her?
Well, she's the one
who started it.
She was being controlled,
which means she's not our enemy.
Think about it.
Don't you have a sacred vow
to not take innocent lives.
[TIO]
Apologies for interrupting.
But could you at
least remove that rod
while you decide my fate?
Huh?
[TIO]
If you leave it inside me,
I'll die no matter
what you choose.
[HAJIME]
Yeah? How so?
[TIO]
When I transform,
you'll be witness to
a beautiful young woman
whose buns have been skewered
by this oversized metal pipe.
Do you think anyone
could survive that?
My mana is running out.
I'm not exactly opposed
to this new sensation
I've been introduced to,
but I also don't want it
to be the death of me.
For the love of all that is
good and holy in this world,
‐‐I beg you, pull it out!
‐‐[HAJIME sighs]
Yeah, yeah. Fine.
[TIO screams]
Could you go a little
slower please?
Oh! I'm not used to this.
You're being so rough.
What is... [moans loudly]
What is this feeling?
Oh!! Something is
stirring deep within me.
Yes. Yes.
That's it. Just a little more.
You overgrown lizard!
[TIO squeals]
[TIO] I asked you
to be gentle with me.
And yet, you showed no mercy.
Never have I experienced this.
Oh. You've spared me.
I'm still in discomfort.
And a humiliating pain
courses through me.
And yet, it's still such
a sweet sensation.
Okay.
[TIO]
Ahem.
My sincerest apologies.
I belong to the Klarus clan
of the dragonborn.
My name is Tio Klarus.
Let's chat.
[AIKO] An army of monsters
is marching on Ur?
[TIO]
Indeed.
The dark‐robed man
I described intends
to use these creatures
to attack the town.
His army numbers well
into the thousands, I fear.
What? How do we stop them?
[HAJIME] This is more than
just a small army of beasts.
I'm counting 50, no,
make that 60 thousand.
They're already making
their way toward the town.
If they keep going at this pace,
they'll arrive in two days time.
Then we have to
go warn everybody.
We can evacuate.
And send for help.
Some backup.
[WILL]
Uh, hey.
Maybe Hajime could do
something about this army?
[gasps]
Nope.
My only responsibility
is getting Will back
to Fuhren safely.
How am I supposed to do that
if I'm fighting a
bunch of monsters?
Say, Nagumo.
Did you see any sign of the man
in the dark robes with them?
No.
I've kept an eye out
while scanning their ranks,
but I haven't seen anyone
like Tio described.
Oh. I see.
Could you, maybe,
look a bit closer?
Don't want to.
‐‐[HAJIME] See ya.
‐‐[yells]
[AIKO]
Nagumo, wait!
[HAJIME]
I just told you that my only job
is getting him back home alive.
The rest of you can
stay here if you want.
But, then, who's gonna warn
Ur of what's coming?
Yes, good point.
Ahem. This overly‐hostile
warrior is right.
Informing the town should
be our highest priority.
I can help.
But give me a day of rest,
so I'll recover to full health.
Oh. I see.
Unfortunately, Hajime
took so much out of me
that I can barely
move right now.
[HAJIME growls]
[moans]
That look makes me feel
like filth personified.
How lewd.
I'm starting to think I
should've killed you after all.
[TIO]
Your words puncture my heart,
just as your fists pummeled
the very core of my being.
And your weapon penetrated
my most personal areas.
My heart, body, and soul
are brimming with pleasure!
[moans]
[groans]
[TIO giggles]
Such horrid treatment.
Such new sensations.
I feel like I might explode.
[shrieks, giggles]
[AIKO]
Hey! Wait!
We're coming, too!
[MELD]
ARIFURETA:
From Commonplace
to World's Strongest.