[HAJIME]
Am I alive?
Or is this what happens
when you die?
It's so dark.
I can't see anything.
Nah. I don't think
I'm dead just yet.
So, am I still in the
Great Orcus Labyrinth?
I fell a long way.
I couldn't have gone
so deep that I'm in
an unexplored area, right?
Either way, I need
to start going up.
There's gotta be some
stairs somewhere.
This level is huge.
Not like any of
the chambers before.
A rabbit? All the way down here?
I thought monsters were
supposed to be tougher
the further down you went.
[growling]
[HAJIME]
Crap. Never mind.
That bunny is a
nightmare beast!
Gah!
It spotted me!
[HAJIME gasps]
[HAJIME yells]
[growling]
[whimpers]
[screams]
[HAJIME]
That bear is huge!
My hunter turned out to be prey!
And I'm next!
[whimpers]
[panting]
[growling]
[grunts]
[grunting]
That bear took my arm!
I think I'm gonna be sick.
He's... He's eating it!
[HAJIME whimpering]
No. Transmute!
Transmute!
Transmute, transmute,
transmute, transmute,
transmute, transmute, transmute!
[HAJIME]
Gotta get away...
[screams]
Please! I don't wanna die!
[HAJIME yelps]
[HAJIME]
But I'm losing blood.
So tired.
Everything's... going black.
[HAJIME]
I'm alive, but how?
Is that...
a Holy Crystal? It is.
A mythical stone created
by mana crystallization.
Formed over a millennia.
"The saturation of mana
creates a liquid
that begins to flow
from the stone.
This liquid is called Holy
Water and has the ability
to heal any injury
and dispel any curse."
Hmm.
I've been visiting the Royal
Library to try to get smarter
so I can actually help
the rest of my classmates.
But I don't know how
much the knowledge I gained
will help me survive if
I can't fight for myself.
I can't fight that
monster, though.
It's way tougher
than the Behemoth.
I never should have entered
this stupid Labyrinth.
Someone, help me!
[MELD]
Listen up!
You'll watch each others'
backs in the Labyrinth.
Help your brethren out,
no matter what.
‐‐Got it?
‐‐Got it!
[growling]
[HAJIME yells]
[KOUKI yells]
See? I'll keep you all safe.
Amanogawa. Thank you.
Why bother with a sword when
you're useless with it?
Best to stay back and
let us handle things.
Nagumo, are you okay?
Yeah.
[KOUKI] You just have to work
harder and keep training.
If I were you, I'd use every
second of downtime I had
to level up my skills.
‐‐[KAORI] Huh?
‐‐[SHIZUKU] Hm?
What is that thing?
Look how shiny it is.
Aw, yeah.
We've stumbled upon
a glanz crystal.
Larger ones like this are rare.
Impressive.
Apparently, they're
pretty popular stones
for engagement rings.
It's beautiful!
[KURAYAMA]
Well, then.
Sounds like somethin'
I should get my hands on.
Get back here!
Don't do that on your own
before we've even checked
if it's safe!
[KURAYAMA yells]
[STUDENTS chattering]
[HAJIME]
Over there!
[STUDENTS chattering]
[STUDENTS yelling]
[KAORI]
It's a monster!
[yelling continues]
[MELD]
It was a trap!
Everyone! Get back to
the stairs, right now!
[STUDENTS chattering]
[KOUKI grunts]
[KOUKI]
Nice one, Shizuku!
[SHIZUKU]
Hurry, you guys!
[gasps]
[KAORI gasps]
[MELD]
Move it. Don't wait for me.
I'm not letting any
of you die down here.
[MELD] O, God, grant
protection to your children.
May the ground itself
repel our enemies.
Let them do no harm.
Deny these monsters passage.
Hallowed Ground!
[growling]
[SOLDIERS grunt]
[KAORI gasps]
[SHIZUKU]
Kaori! Run!
[KAORI gasps]
[SHIZUKU]
Transmute?
‐‐[KAORI] Nagumo!
‐‐[HAJIME] Go!
Now's your chance to escape!
[growling]
Fast thinking. Well done.
This won't hold him for long.
You should go now.
Get Shirasaki to safety.
Please, Captain Meld!
[HAJIME]
Hurry!
[MELD]
I swear we'll rescue you.
Be strong. I'll be back.
[HAJIME]
It's no good.
[MELD] Get out of there, kid!
We'll cover you!
Ready, everyone?
[STUDENTS]
Ready!
MELD]
Run! Quickly!
[HAJIME]
Got it!
Why? Why? Why? Why?
I should be dead now. Gone!
But I don't wanna die.
It'd be easier.
I'm alone in the dark.
But I don't want to.
I don't want to die!
Even though it might
be for the best!
Dammit!
My left arm hurts so much.
Why is it in so much pain when
it's not even there anymore?
How did this happen?
Why did I fall?
Who did this to me?!
I wanna know who, dammit!
I swear, we'll rescue you.
Fire!
Second volley! Fire!
Keep running! You'll make it!
[HAJIME]
Is that blast targeting me?!
[screams]
[HAJIME]
It doesn't make sense.
I don't know why anyone
would try to kill me.
But that spell was
aimed directly at me.
I have no doubt about that.
So who cast it?
Him.
For what reason?
Guess it doesn't matter anymore.
[MELD]
Run!
[SHIZUKU]
Get outta there!
[CLASSMATE 1A]
What happened?
Did someone hit him?
‐‐Nagumo!
‐‐Don't!
But he's alone out there!
[HAJIME screams]
[KAORI]
No!
[HAJIME]
Shirasaki?
It's the middle of the night.
I'm sorry, but‐‐
But I don't want you to
go with us when we train
down in the Labyrinth.
It's just‐‐
I had a terrible
nightmare, and I‐‐
I think something bad'll happen.
[HAJIME]
Hold on. What?
Yes! We were in
a dark place, and...
You wouldn't say anything
when I called to you.
There was just this silence.
Then... after that...
Go on.
[KAORI]
You disappeared.
[HAJIME]
I see.
In that case...
Will you protect me?
[KAORI gasps]
[HAJIME] My Synergist job
is super commonplace,
and unfortunately, not really
well‐suited to combat.
But you're a Priest, Shirasaki.
So then...
If I do get hurt,
you can just use your
powers to heal me.
[KAORI] Okay.
I promise I'll protect you.
You'll be safe.
[KAORI]
No!
[HAJIME] Nobody's going to
rescue me all the way down here.
So what am I supposed to do?
Why should I have to suffer
such a horrible fate?
What did I do?
I don't deserve this!
I was brought to this world
in some crazy turn of events.
Then my classmates betrayed me.
The monsters here are too
powerful for me to fight.
I'm trapped in a metaphorical
and literal pit of despair.
So what next?
I want to survive and go home.
Which makes anything between
me and my goal the enemy.
That's right.
If something's in the way,
if anyone's keeping me
from my destination...
...I'll kill 'em.
I'm so thirsty. Hungry, too.
[gulping]
Right. I don't care if I
have to eat a damn monster.
I'll freakin' do it.
[growling]
Yeah, that's right!
You're gonna be food for
me now, you overgrown mutts!
Now shut up and die already.
The monsters around here
are pretty damn resilient.
[grunting]
[HAJIME] Man, this is way
grosser than I imagined.
[gasping]
What the hell?
Feels like something's
burning me from the inside!
[gasps, screams]
[splashing]
[coughing]
[HAJIME]
Why won't it stop?
What the hell is happening?
[screams]
Shit, do you die
if you eat monster meat?
[gasping, grunting]
[yells]
[HAJIME] I think I'd be
screwed without this Holy Water.
I'd have died when that monster
meat tore my guts apart.
But now, it's strange.
I don't feel any pain.
My body actually feels lighter.
What was that feeling?
Is it gone for good?
Holy crap, I look like a demon.
Huh. Okay.
Let me check my status plate.
Looks like eating monster
meat bumped my level up.
And I've got some new skills.
Let's see here.
I guess Mana Manipulation is
exactly what it sounds like.
Huh.
I didn't even need
to say the spell.
Who knew that choking down
monster meat would do this.
It's like a training shortcut.
Lightning field?
That move. Whoa. Check it out.
The mana's turning redder,
just like the monsters'.
I can't shoot it like that
two‐tailed wolf did,
but if I can manipulate the
voltage and not overdo it...
Smells like crap, but it's
better than eating the meat
raw again.
I've got food and water.
What I need now is
some kind of weapon.
Nice!
I can identify a rock
just by grabbing it now.
I should be able to
make something useful
if I implement that
the right way.
Taur Stone. A solid black rock.
Hardness ranked at eight.
Toughness, eight.
Strong against physical
force and heat,
but weak against the cold.
Fragile when frozen.
Add heat to bond
with components.
Wow! Blast rock.
A flammable stone.
Can explode when pressure
and heat are applied
in a confined space.
Sounds like gunpowder.
With enough volume and pressure,
explosions rival the highest
tier of fire magic spells.
And that's how you make bullets.
A six‐shot revolver and ammo,
both crafted from extremely
tough Taur Stone.
Each bullet packed
with Blast Rock powder.
Now, add a dash
of Lightning Field.
I'd better give my new
best friend a good name.
Huh. I've got it.
You're Donner.
[HAJIME chewing]
[grunts, spits]
This meat's not any tastier.
Now to see if it was worth it.
Good, my stats increased.
Looks like whenever I eat a
monster I haven't had before,
the numbers go up a lot.
Maybe these new skills
will help me find a way
outta this place.
Quick step.
That's the teleportation.
Aerodynamics.
That's how it
pushed off in midair.
Now that I'm stronger,
I should pay someone a visit.
[growling]
[HAJIME]
Hey. Long time no see.
You never told me
how my arm tasted.
Straight down to business, huh?
Well, that's fine with me.
This time,
you're gonna get eaten!
[growling]
[HAJIME]
Quick Step!
Ha. That's right.
I'm a real threat now.
Not just some weak, sniveling
prey for you to hunt down.
Aerodynamics!
[growling]
Hold still‐‐Gah!
I'm real proud of this one.
Take a closer look!
[growling]
You taste terrible.
Although, I gotta admit it's
an oddly satisfying mouthful
to swallow.
[growling]
You're done.
Now, then.
Time to get out
of this Labyrinth.
I'm gonna survive this nightmare
and find my way back home.
And I don't care
who stands in my way.
They try me, I'll kill 'em.
[YUE]
Arifureta:
From Commonplace
to World's Strongest.