[MONSTER ARMY growling]
[AIKO] Nagumo, is there anything
you can do about this army
of monsters?
[AIKO]
Please, Nagumo.
There must be something
you can do for us!
Without your help,
those creatures will destroy
the entire town, and hundreds
of innocent lives will be lost.
That's unexpected.
I thought you prioritized
the safety of your students
above all else,
but now you're
asking one of them
to put his life
on the line.
For a bunch of strangers.
Of course, as a teacher,
I should always put
my students first.
That said...
I don't want to cast aside
the many people of this world
who I've come
to know and respect.
I know I wasn't there for you
when you needed me the most,
so these words may not
mean very much to you.
But I'll say them anyway.
Nagumo, I do not want your
life to be an empty one.
And it will be if you forget
how to care about other people.
Ms. Aiko,
no matter what happens,
you'll still be
my teacher, right?
Yes, always!
No matter what
decision I might make.
Even if it's the opposite
of what you would've wanted?
That's right.
Provided that you listened
carefully to what I had to say
to you before you
arrived at your decision.
Uh, where are you going?
[HAJIME]
There's an army headed this way.
I should probably start
getting ready for 'em.
So then you'll help us?
[HAJIME] Only 'cause
my teacher told me to.
[AIKO] Nagumo!
I thought I'd find you here.
Are there any last‐minute
preparations I can help with?
[HAJIME]
Nah, everything should be good.
Not long now. The monsters
are gonna reach us soon.
Heh, I can practically
hear you frowning.
Don't worry. It'll be fine.
I realize that I have no right
to say this since I'm the one
who asked you to fight
them in the first place.
But come back safe, okay?
[YUUKA]
Do you have a second?
[HAJIME]
What's up, Sonobe?
I just want to say thank
you for what you did for me.
Huh? What are you
talking about?
Well, you might not
even remember it,
but you saved my life back
when we were in the labyrinth.
And I never got the
chance to thank you.
[HAJIME]
I saved your life?
It was probably just a fluke.
Even if it was,
I owe you.
You gave me a chance,
and I am not gonna waste it.
[HAJIME]
Okay.
[YUUKA]
Well, see ya.
[HAJIME]
Sonobe.
Try not to die in this fight.
You're a brave one.
Well, for the most part.
Thanks for that.
Come out.
If you're gonna hide, at least
do a halfway decent job of it.
[TIO gasps]
I was waiting for the right
time to present myself.
Ahem. Um, a moment, please?
A moment, please?
I only wish to make
a trifling request of you.
I promise I shan't
keep you long.
Y‐You're ignoring me!
And it's setting my
nether parts ablaze! Ah!
Oh, such sweet torment!
I never knew neglect
could arouse me like this.
Jeez. This freak.
Well? What do you want,
dragon girl?
You see, I've been thinking.
After we lay waste
to these monsters,
you will continue
on your journey, yes?
[HAJIME]
Yeah.
[TIO]
As I suspected.
Now, if I might join you
on said journey‐‐
[HAJIME]
Nope.
Ugh! A denial as
swift as it is cruel!
I swear that I
wouldn't be a burden.
I'd fall at your feet
and call you Master,
and offer myself to you,
body and soul!
Or instead, you could
go back to whatever
dark hole you crawled out of.
That harsh stare‐‐
it pierces through me!
I beg you, Master,
observe how I fight in the
coming battle before you decide.
I assure you, my performance
will be more than satisfactory.
You will surely ask me to
join you after witnessing it,
I just know it!
Why haven't we
gotten rid of her?
Because, she'll be
an asset in battle.
There they are.
[MONSTER ARMY growling]
All right,
time to put on a show.
What do you mean?
I'll give a little speech.
See if I can't boost
Ms. Aiko's reputation.
Make these people love her.
The more important she seems,
the more influence
she'll have in this world.
I get it.
And since you're her student,
she can use that to help you.
Exactly.
[TOWNSPEOPLE gasp]
Hear me!
Brave citizens of Ur,
there is no need to fear!
Our victory against the foe
is already guaranteed.
[TOWNSPEOPLE chattering]
Because, you see, a goddess,
summoned by the
heavens themselves,
stands among us in human form.
Yes, you know her well.
The Goddess of Plenty.
Lady Aiko.
As long we have her on
our side, we will not fall!
Whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa.
What in the world
are you talking about?
Listen to me.
I am Lady Aiko's
sword and shield.
She has asked me to
protect the town of Ur,
and I hereby swear
I will heed her command.
For Lady Aiko!
[TOWNSPEOPLE]
Lady Aiko!
[cheering]
[HAJIME] Witness the power
of the Goddess's blade.
One who's been blessed
by the Lady herself.
[TOWNSPEOPLE gasp]
[TOWNSPEOPLE cheer]
They don't stand a chance.
[SHEA]
I'm ready to go!
[MONSTER ARMY growling]
He may have said this
ring was a mana reserve
made from a Holy Crystal...
...but we both know the truth.
What a bold gesture, proposing
to me right before battle.
[HAJIME]
Hey.
That ring's only a loan,
so don't get attached to it.
Please don't take it back!
The sorrow will surely kill me!
I expect you to drain
that reserve till it's dry.
Let's see what those
dragon powers can do.
But of course.
You have only to give
the order, Master.
Let's take these bastards out!
[MONSTER ARMY growling]
[TIO]
Ooh! It's ecstasy!
I can feel my master's
love flowing through me.
Now blow, tempest winds.
Pour forth, torrential flame.
Flame Tempest!
[YUE chuckles]
[TOWNSPEOPLE cheer]
[MONSTER ARMY growling]
Who's next?
Bring it on!
[MONSTER ARMY growling]
[TIO grunts] It seems this is
where I must stop.
Huh? Ah!
Not my engagement ring!
Not bad for a masochistic perv.
Take a nap,
I'll handle the rest.
[TIO snoring]
[HAJIME]
Well, crap. Outta bullets.
Yue. You got much mana left?
No. I've only got a few
more spells left in me.
Gravitic magic uses
up a lot of mana.
It's fine, don't sweat it.
Use what you've got
left on the big guys.
Right!
You can reward me later.
[HAJIME]
Follow me, bunny.
[SHEA]
Aye aye, Captain!
Lightning Wyrm!
[SHEA]
Woohoo!
[MONSTER ARMY growls]
[HAJIME]
Shea!
Can you tell the difference
between these beasts?
It looks like some of them
are being controlled,
just like Tio was.
The rest are totally low‐level.
[HAJIME]
That's right.
[HAJIME] The brainwashed ones
are most likely being controlled
by one person.
If we can take him out, we win.
[SHEA]
I get it.
They'll wake up
confused and run away!
[SHEA yells]
[MONSTER ARMY growls]
[OGRE 10A growls]
[MONSTER ARMY growling]
[SHEA yelling]
[SHEA yells]
[SHEA grunts]
[WOLF 10A growls]
[HAJIME]
Sorry, man.
But you picked the
wrong guy to mess with.
‐‐[GUY yells]
‐‐[WOLF 10B growls]
[SHIMIZU grunts]
Kinda expected a demon
to be leading this army.
I don't believe it‐‐
why would one of my students
do something so
completely horrible?
I just wanted to show
everybody in this world
how incredible I am.
What?
That makes no sense.
All this just made you
look evil, Shimizu.
Why would you think we'd be
impressed by you hurting people?
Not you, stupid.
I mean the demons.
[GROUP gasps]
I went north into the
mountains alone to prove
that I could capture a monster.
That's when it happened.
I met an actual demon.
They understood exactly
what I was capable of.
They could see how much
potential was inside me.
So, naturally, I had to make
a little contract with them.
[AIKO]
A contract?
What is it they want from you?
It's funny that you should ask.
'Cause it says I
have to murder you.
[GROUP gasps]
[SHIMIZU] They can't leave
the Goddess of Plenty
to her own devices.
She'd end up being more
of a nuisance than
the so‐called heroes.
Which means that if I kill you,
the demons will be so
pleased that they'll hail me
as their champion.
[AIKO]
Please say you're joking.
How did this go wrong?!
I had 60,000 troops,
but I still lost?
Why the hell do you have
such powerful weapons?
Tell me!
What kind of monster are you?
I understand what you're saying.
You just want to feel like
a special, important person.
It's a perfectly natural desire.
But still.
You can't join the
demons to achieve that.
You shut up!
Why shouldn't I choose
to be on the side
that'll treat me better?
Because you know it's not right.
I'm sure that deep down your
intentions are pure and noble.
And I won't let one of my
students be used for evil!
You don't know what I feel.
Shimizu.
Why don't we start over
again from the beginning?
I promise I'll always
have your back.
[SHIMIZU sniffling]
Everything's gonna
to be all right.
[GROUP gasps]
[YUUKA]
Ms. Aiko!
Nobody move!
Or I'll kill her!
This needle is coated
in a powerful poison I got
from a monster.
Drop your weapons and put
your hands up or she's dead.
Please. Shimizu.
You don't wanna do this!
Don't tell me what I wanna do,
you damn hypocrite.
Keep quiet and be a good hostage
so I can get the
hell out of here!
Hey, tough guy.
[HAJIME]
Hmm?
[SHIMIZU] Yeah, I'm talkin'
to you, edgelord.
[HAJIME groans]
Stop playing stupid.
You keep looking around and
our teacher is seriously dead.
[HAJIME sighs]
You sure you got
the balls for that?
[SHIMIZU]
You're asking for it.
[HAJIME]
Fine, fine, what do you want?
[SHIMIZU] Gimme your gun,
and all your other weapons
while you're at it.
Yeah, I had a feeling that's
how this was gonna play out.
[SHIMIZU]
Just hand them over, dammit!
Afraid I can't do that.
Besides, if you take her
back to the demons,
they're just gonna end
up killing her anyway.
So what's the point in me
giving up my stuff, huh?
Seriously, man,
the guns, right now!
[SHEA]
Look out!
[SHIMIZU grunts]
[SHEA, AIKO grunt]
Shea!
[HAJIME growls]
Drink this!
No. Please help
your teacher first.
He scratched her!
[AIKO whimpers]
This looks pretty bad.
Gotta be fast.
Ms. Aiko?
How's that? Better?
I take it the medicine worked?
No. I don't wanna die.
Please help me!
This wasn't the plan.
I can't go out like this.
Shimizu!
Oh, no!
Nagumo, quick.
Give him some medicine.
You remember he just
tried to kill you, right?
[AIKO] I promised no matter
what happened in this world,
I would always do my best
to protect my students.
You have to help me! Save him!
Shimizu.
Be honest.
Are you my enemy?
No! Of course I'm not!
I'll swear my loyalty to you!
I'll do whatever you want.
Just let me live.
Please, no!
[gunshots]
How could you?
[HAJIME]
He was lying.
Not true.
You heard what he said!
[HAJIME] You think he's
magically reformed?
Sorry, but I'm not
some bleeding heart.
I don't believe
in crap like that.
You could've saved him,
but you chose death?
Exactly.
I killed one of your
precious students.
I thought over what you said.
But I won't let my enemies live.
You see.
I don't have any mercy
left inside of me.
Understand? Not a drop.
[AIKO]
Shimizu... No...
[HAJIME]
You want a reason?
I told you. He was our enemy.
[WILL]
That's not why you did it.
If you hadn't shot him,
he still would've been dead
in minutes.
Didn't realize you were
paying that much attention.
Hajime.
You're so nice to your teacher.
[SHEA] That shot that got
Shimizu was actually aimed
at Aiko, wasn't it?
But since you killed him,
she doesn't have to think
he died because of an attack
meant for her.
[TIO] It would've broken
her heart, but now,
she can still be the
profoundly caring teacher
she always was.
[YUE]
You know...
Aiko will realize what you did.
And I think...
...her words had a
profound impact on you.
They're in your blood now.
[MYU]
ARIFURETA:
From Commonplace
to World's Strongest.