[HAJIME] Yue, the weapons
and powers I've got now,
they'll draw attention.
Especially from the Holy Church.
I doubt they'll be
very accepting.
It might just be us
against the world.
And honestly, I'm not sure
if we have enough lives
saved up to survive it.
[YUE]
We may not.
[HAJIME chuckles]
But if I look out for you,
and if you look out for me,
nobody can stop us.
Nobody.
All right.
We'll beat everything
and everyone.
And bust out of this
crappy world together.
[HAJIME] One seemingly ordinary
day, we suddenly found ourselves
in the world of Tortus,
where we had been summoned
by Ehit, the god of creation.
According to Pope Ishtar, there
are three races of creatures
who inhabit this world.
They are the humans,
the demons, and the beastmen.
For centuries, human and
demon‐kind had been engaged
in a bloody war, with neither
side gaining the advantage.
But then, the demons
learned to control monsters,
tipping the scales
in their favor,
and pushing humanity to
the brink of destruction.
To prevent humankind's
fall, Ehit,
worshipped by the
people of this world,
summoned heroes with incredible
power to this kingdom.
[ISHTAR]
On behalf of the entire kingdom,
allow me to say what
an honor it is
to have you brave
heroes here among us.
The people in this kingdom
are in danger of annihilation.
We can't let them die!
We were brought here to fight,
and I say that we do it!
No! Amanogawa, you can't!
I understand why
you want to help,
but please think about what
they're asking you to do.
Your lives would be in danger!
I'll fight, too.
I wouldn't want you to
have to go it all alone.
[KOUKI]
Are you sure?
Yeah, count me in.
I don't see what
other option we have.
That's great!
[KAORI] And, um... If Shizuku's
going to fight the demons,
then I'll try to help, too.
[KOUKI]
Thanks, Kaori!
[AIKO]
You can't do this!
[HAJIME] In Tortus, some job
classes are combat‐oriented
and some... aren't.
My classmates were all summoned
with extremely rare jobs
that lent them extraordinary
fighting abilities
and unbelievable power.
But my class, Synergist,
isn't combat‐oriented.
It's more like being this
world's version of a blacksmith.
My status points are
depressingly average.
[HAJIME]
Shirasaki?
It's the middle of the night.
I'm sorry, but‐‐
but I don't want you to
go with us when we train
down in the Labyrinth.
It's just‐‐
I had a terrible
nightmare, and I‐‐
I think something bad'll happen.
[HAJIME]
Hold on. What?
Yes! We were in
a dark place, and...
You wouldn't say anything
when I called to you.
There was just this silence.
Then, after that...
You disappeared.
[HAJIME]
I see.
In that case...
Will you protect me?
[KAORI gasps]
[HAJIME] My Synergist job
is super commonplace,
and unfortunately, not really
well‐suited to combat.
But you're a Priest, Shirasaki.
So then...
If I do get hurt,
you can just use your
powers to heal me.
[HAJIME] We were sent to
the Great Orcus Labyrinth
with members of the Royal
Guard to do some training.
[MELD] Help your brethren
out, no matter what.
Got it?
[STUDENTS]
Got it!
What is that thing?
Look how shiny it is!
[HIYAMA yells]
[STUDENTS chattering]
[CLASSMATE 5.5A]
What's that?
[STUDENTS yelling]
[MELD]
Run! Quickly!
[HAJIME]
Got it!
[HAJIME] In the midst of
battling the Behemoth,
one of my classmates
betrayed me,
and I was plunged
into the abyss.
[HAJIME]
Is that blast targeting me?
[screams]
What did I do?
I don't deserve this!
I was brought to this world
in some crazy turn of events.
Then my classmates betrayed me.
I'm trapped in a metaphorical
and literal pit of despair.
So what next?
I want to survive and go home.
Which makes anything between
me and my goal the enemy.
That's right.
If something's in the way...
If anyone's keeping me
from my destination...
I'll kill 'em.
I'm so thirsty. Hungry, too.
Right.
I don't care if I have
to eat a damn monster.
I'll freakin' do it.
[HAJIME] I decided I'd do
anything it took to survive.
I managed to use my Synergist
powers to kill a monster.
Yeah, that's right!
You're gonna be food for me now,
you overgrown mutts!
[gasps]
What the hell?
It feels like something's
burning me from the inside.
[screaming]
[coughing]
Why won't it stop?
What the hell is happening?
[HAJIME] The Holy Water
I drank kept me alive
as the monster meat
transformed my body,
strengthening it and
increasing my power.
[HAJIME screaming]
[HAJIME]
Taur Stone.
A solid black rock.
Hardness ranked at eight.
Toughness, eight.
Strong against
physical force and heat,
but weak against the cold.
Fragile when frozen.
Add heat to bond
with components.
Wow!
Blast rock.
A flammable stone.
Can explode when pressure
and heat are applied
in a confined space.
Sounds like gunpowder.
With enough volume and pressure,
explosions rival the highest
tier of fire magic spells.
And that's how you make bullets.
A six‐shot revolver and ammo,
both crafted from
extremely tough Taur Stone.
Each bullet packed with
Blast Rock powder.
Now, add a dash
of Lightning Field.
I'd better give my new
best friend a good name.
Huh. I've got it.
You're Donner.
Now that I'm stronger...
I should pay someone a visit.
Wielding the modern
weapon I'd crafted
with my Synergist skills,
I set my sights on home.
Now, then.
Time to get out
of this Labyrinth.
I'm gonna survive this nightmare
and find my way back home.
And I don't care
who stands in my way.
They try me, I'll kill 'em.
[HAJIME groans]
I've got nothing.
I studied a ton back
at the castle,
but I don't remember seeing
anything like this before.
Guess that could
mean it's really ancient.
Damn it!
[RED CYCLOPS growls]
[BLUE CYCLOPS growls]
[HAJIME]
Lookin' for me?
[BLUE CYCLOPS growls]
Okay, let's find out
what you and your buddy
were protecting.
[YUE]
Wait! Please, help me!
[HAJIME]
Not happening.
[YUE]
Please. I'll do anything!
You're wrong. It's not my fault.
Listen. I'm here because
I was betrayed.
[HAJIME]
Damn it.
[sighs] I'm gonna regret
this later, aren't I?
[HAJIME grunts]
This thing really
doesn't wanna let go.
But I'm not as weak
as I used to be!
Can I ask your name?
I'm Hajime. Hajime Nagumo.
[YUE]
Hajime. Hajime, Hajime.
[HAJIME]
What's yours?
You've got a name, right?
Give me one.
What? You want me
to give you one?
Did you forget yours
or something?
[YUE] I don't need my
old name anymore.
I want one that you choose!
Um, how about Yue?
[YUE]
Yue?
Uh‐huh.
Where I come from, it's a
word that means "moon."
[YUE]
Moon?
[HAJIME] When I first walked in,
this room looked like
it was filled with stars,
and your golden hair
reminded me of the moon
in the night sky.
Sound good?
Perfect.
It sounds perfect!
Thank you!
It's no problem.
Here, this is for you.
[YUE]
I don't need it.
Oh, sure, I guess a vampire
who was sealed away
for 300 years wouldn't.
Don't you ever
feel hungry though?
[YUE]
I was before, but I'm fine now.
Did you eat something?
I must've missed that somehow.
[YUE]
I drank your blood.
Oh, whoa.
So if you have blood,
then you don't have to consume
anything else to survive?
[YUE] I could get
nutrients from normal food.
But blood is the more
effective way for me to feed.
Interesting.
[HAJIME]
Uh...
[YUE chuckles]
[HAJIME growls]
Not cool!
Keep it up, Hajime.
You are way too calm right now!
I think they're kind of cute.
Are you kidding me?!
And why was the one
earlier trampling them?
[HAJIME growls]
[YUE]
Hajime. Run!
[YUE grunts]
[YUE]
Hajime, don't worry about me.
Just shoot!
Yue.
[PLANT MONSTER 3A growls]
Take the shot. Do it!
Uh... Seriously?
That makes everything easier!
[YUE gasps]
[PLANT MONSTER 3A shrieks]
How 'bout I rearrange
that ugly mug?
[PLANT MONSTER 3A shrieks]
[HAJIME] If there's something
here, it's behind these doors.
Are you scared?
[YUE]
No.
Not as long as I'm with you.
[HAJIME]
That's what a like to hear.
[YUE gasps]
[HAJIME grunting]
[YUE]
Hajime.
[HAJIME]
Yue... she's crying.
[growling]
[YUE]
I failed you. I'm sorry.
Hey, stop crying. 'Kay?
You did great.
[HAJIME grunts]
I've prepared a little
something special for you.
This is for hurting Yue!
[BEAST shrieks]
Azure Blaze!
Greetings, my name
is Oscar Orcus,
and I am the man who
built this labyrinth.
I congratulate you on
surviving my trials.
I assume the term "Maverick"
is familiar to you?
So you're him.
[OSCAR] I've no doubt you
have a great many questions.
Unfortunately, what you're
seeing is only a recording.
So I'm afraid that your
queries must go unanswered.
Instead, I wish to pass
along an important truth.
A truth about the history
of this war‐torn world,
one that inspired myself
and others like me
to stand up and fight for
what we believed was right.
[HAJIME gasping]
What's happening?
It's like something's
being imprinted on my mind!
[HAJIME grunting]
[grunting continues]
Holy shit.
Hajime?
The legends are wrong.
The Mavericks weren't evil,
they were Liberators. Till...
It's so warm.
Hey, what're you doing?
I'm pretty sure I said
I wanted to bathe alone.
[YUE chuckles]
You could at least
cover up a little.
There were lots of
towels back there.
But I want you to look.
You're killin' me here, Yue.
See, the thing is...
What's wrong?
You don't think I'm pretty?
No, that's not it.
I think you're totally gorgeous.
Well, good.
[YUE]
All of me is yours, Hajime.
So there's no point
in being shy.
[gasps]
You're just... I, um... I...
Ah...! So naked!
[YUE giggles]
Ah... oh! Oh, wow,
I can feel it touching me.
Feel what?
[HAJIME]
You're kidding, right?
Know what?
Forget it, I'm out of here.
[YUE]
I don't think so.
[HAJIME]
Hey! No! Hold on!
[yells]
[SHEA whines]
How much longer am
I gonna have to wait?
Seriously, would they
just show up already?
[sighs]
[growling]
[SHEA]
Here they come!
[KOUKI]
Arifureta:
From Commonplace
to World's Strongest.