[HAJIME sighs]
All this says is that the
entrance to the labyrinth
is in Reisen Gorge.
Thanks for nothing, mapmaker.
[SHEA]
Uh‐huh.
Sure, uh, whatever.
What's wrong?
Why are you squirming like that?
Um... I just...
...need to go powder
my nose pretty badly.
You won't find a
bathroom down here.
[SHEA]
Aww...
[HAJIME] Anyway, since we
can walk through the gorge
on the way to Gryuen,
we may as well hit up
the labyrinth if we can find it.
[SHEA]
Hajime!
I found something
I think you'll like!
Quick, come look over here!
[SHEA]
See? Isn't it weird?
[MILEDI] Hi, there!
Glad to meet you!
Let me be the first to welcome
you to Miledi Reisen's
Super Duper Exciting Labyrinth!
What? Where is that
voice coming from?
Who cares, it's the entrance
you were looking for!
Now our adventure
can really begin.
So... Do you
think this is legit?
Mm‐hmm.
Why's that?
Miledi was in Oscar's notes.
Okay.
Now, how are we
supposed to get inside?
Dunno.
It's probably complicated.
[SHEA yelps]
You're kidding.
Where'd she go?
[YUE]
Ugh.
The bunny wet herself.
[SHEA whines]
Don't look. Let's pretend
this never happened.
[MILEDI]
Did that scare ya?
Gave you quite
a fright, didn't it?
Gonna cry to your mommy?
Wah, wah! [giggles]
Looks like it's about
time for me to test out
that thing you made me,
right, Hajime?
[SHEA yells]
[MILEDI]
Aww, nice try!
But these stone tablets will
automatically regenerate
after a certain amount of time.
I'm thinking Miledi Reisen
wasn't one of the Liberators
after all.
She's just a scourge
on humanity.
I have to agree.
[SHEA growls]
[HAJIME] It didn't seem like
this was going to end up being
a real labyrinth,
but it's definitely
got some maze vibes.
[HAJIME gasps]
[rumbling]
Stop!
Just as I thought,
we're not able to use
projectile magic in this place.
Well, that's lame.
Let me handle these balls!
[yelling]
[SHEA grunts]
Done!
Hurry, now's your
chance to pass!
[HAJIME]
Got it.
[SHEA yells]
We made it through!
[MILEDI]
How're you doing?
It looks like you might be
getting a bit of a headache.
[laughs]
[MILEDI]
Uh‐oh!
The floor in here
is ooey‐gooey gross!
[laughs]
[SHEA groans]
[MILEDI] Hey!
How's your day going, huh?
[SHEA]
That stupid witch!
If she makes fun
of me one more time...
[HAJIME] I feel like we've
seen this place before.
Don't you?
[YUE]
Definitely.
The puddle's still here.
[SHEA groans]
So are we back
in the first room?
Looks like it.
[MILEDI]
Guys!
Tell me how you feel right now.
Go on, don't be shy!
[SHEA grunting]
[YUUKA]
So, Nia.
Tell me, when is Ms. Aiko
heading out on her expedition?
I believe that she's
been scheduled to depart
sometime in the next
few days, ma'am.
[YUUKA sighs]
It's all happening so quickly.
But... I guess...
We'd just get sad if
she stayed here any longer.
[NANA]
Hey, Yuuka.
That's a weird look
on your face, heh.
So do you have
something on your mind?
[YUUKA]
Yeah.
I've been thinking, and I can't
keep sitting around here
doing nothing all day.
So I've decided that I'm
going to go with Ms. Aiko.
Hey. Have you
gone crazy or what?
That's a terrible idea.
I assure you that
I've thought about this.
It isn't a sudden decision.
Honestly, I've been feeling
this way for a while now.
Ever since Nagumo died.
Sure, I'm scared, and
confused about some things.
But I have to do something.
Surely you guys feel
the same way, right?
Seriously?
It isn't safe out there.
No! You could end up
exactly like he did.
You said it. He's dead.
All because he tried
to be brave.
Yes, but if he
hadn't acted bravely,
I wouldn't even be
standing here today.
Not just me.
Nagumo saved each
and every one of us.
Yeah. I guess so.
Besides...
I'm not saying any of
you have to go with me.
Stay here, but I refuse
to waste any more time.
Wait, Yuuka.
Are you sure?
Look, I don't have the guts
to go with Amanogawa
and the others.
So the least I can do
is keep Ms. Aiko safe.
[HAJIME panting]
Now that is an impressive door.
I'm pretty sure we just stumbled
upon Miledi's chamber.
Yes.
Well, shit, I wish we
had time to celebrate.
Problem is, I've got a
real bad feeling about
these suits of armor
lining the walls.
Don't worry about it.
At least we know what to expect.
Does that mean they're gonna
come to life and attack us?
Hey. Ms. Runny rabbit.
[SHEA]
Um... Yes? What is it?
You're a tough bunny.
You can handle
yourself in a fight.
So get in there
and have some fun.
We'll save you if it starts
to look like you're gonna die.
I take care of my pupils.
Aw, guys. That's so sweet!
Right! I'll beat the
heck out of Miledi!
[SHEA yelling]
[YUE] Carelessness
will get you killed.
Or punished by me.
I know! I'm... sorry!
[SHEA grunts]
Take this!
[HAJIME]
There's no end to 'em.
[SHEA yelling]
Everyone, quick, jump!
[MILEDI]
Hi, there!
Look at you,
comin' all this way.
This has to be some
kind of joke, right?
Oh, perfect. A giant.
Yeah. This definitely
feels like the big boss.
[MILEDI]
I'm everyone's favorite!
Miledi Reisen, at your service!
[HAJIME]
Who are you really?
Miledi Reisen was human and
would be long dead by now.
We read about her
in Oscar's notebook.
[MILEDI] Ooh! Oh, my gosh,
are you the ones who made it
through Oskie's labyrinth?
I'm the one asking
the questions around here.
If you don't feel
like answering me,
I'll just have to fight you.
We've come down here
to find ancient magic,
and we'll destroy anyone
who gets in our way.
[MILEDI]
I'm telling the truth!
I'm the real Miledi Reisen!
Promise!
If you want to know more,
you better start being
a little friendlier.
[MILEDI] What do you want
this ancient magic for?
It must be something important.
My goal is pretty simple.
I want to get back to my home.
The only reason I'm here is
because of some insane god.
So trust me, I'm not
in this world by choice.
[MILEDI]
I see.
That must've been tough on you.
[HAJIME] We're looking for
a form of ancient magic
that allows you
to jump between worlds.
Because I have no intention
of putting my life
on the line for this one.
That's my answer.
So, will the ancient magic
in this labyrinth
let me get to my world?
[MILEDI]
Hmm, let's see.
Nope! I don't think
I'm gonna tell you!
Then die!
Destroy her core!
That should be like her heart.
[SHEA yells]
[MILEDI]
Wow.
You're pretty good.
[HAJIME]
You think so?
[MILEDI]
Whoa, and fast, too.
[HAJIME]
How's this feel?
Did it work?
It felt like it did, but...
I really hope that was
the end of this fight.
[MILEDI]
Nah.
All your attack did
was tickle me.
Good thing this labyrinth is
sapping your weapon's power.
Shit, her armor.
It's Azantium.
[MILEDI]
The hardest metal in the world.
Now, how about another round?
Watch out! Above us!
[MILEDI laughs]
Let's play a game.
The objective is not
to get squished!
Not good!
Both of you, grab on!
[SHEA]
Okay!
[HAJIME]
They just keep coming!
[MILEDI]
Aw. They couldn't handle it.
But I guess if they couldn't
get past me, there's no way
they'd be able to beat
those bastard gods.
[HAJIME]
I have no interest in doing so.
I told you,
I just want to leave.
[MILEDI]
How'd you get up there?
Why bother telling you?
I've finished my job
as the decoy.
[YUE]
Force Rupture!
[MILEDI] You're not gonna beat
me, you mean, wannabe bullies.
My arms can regenerate
and fix themselves!
See?
Not if we don't let up on you.
[MILEDI]
That move again?
There's no way you're
getting through my armor.
[HAJIME]
I know!
[YUE]
Freeze! Crystal Coffin!
That should keep
her from moving.
This is the part where you die!
[MILEDI laughs]
Looks like you'll need
to be a little stronger.
You see, down here,
your magic isn't as powerful.
Shea!
Finish her off!
[SHEA yelling]
[MILEDI screaming]
Nice work, you guys.
Rabbit.
Bend down for me.
Hajime won't pet you.
So I'll do it instead.
Don't bunnies like that?
You did a good job, Shea.
[SHEA]
Aww!
Aw, Yue. Thank you.
Really.
I was so scared!
I didn't think we were
gonna stop that giant!
[crying]
[gasps]
Hold on a second!
Just now...
She called me by my name!
Hurray!
[MILEDI]
Uh, hey.
Sorry to ruin the love‐fest
you're having, but...
Hi.
I don't understand.
We destroyed your core.
[MILEDI] I used the last of my
energy to buy us enough time
to have a little chat.
I don't wanna hear
anything you have to say.
Die already.
Well, it's less of a chat
and more of a warning.
You said you were going
to get all the Liberators'
ancient magic to achieve
your goal, right?
Then there's something
I wanna say.
[HAJIME]
Okay, shoot.
[MILEDI]
Good luck.
Well, isn't that nice
from the killer tin can.
[MILEDI] The thing is, those
gods we tried to take down
are some really
super‐duper bad guys.
So, I just wanted you
to know what you were
getting yourselves into.
[HAJIME]
Wait. Back it up.
Why're you acting like
we're going to end up
fighting these gods?
[MILEDI]
Because you will.
Because you are who you are.
One day...
You will become the God‐Killer.
[HAJIME]
You're not making sense.
The only way I'll bother
taking them out
is if they get in my way.
[MILEDI chuckles]
That's fine.
Tell yourself whatever you want.
The decisions you make
will surely make this world
a better, happier
place in the end.
Well, look at that.
I think she's finally going.
[MILEDI]
Have fun.
I hope you're able
to live your lives
with all the freedom
that you could ask for.
Hi there, buddies!
Surprise! It's Miledi!
Your best friend!
[laughs] Didn't you enjoy
the dramatic speech I gave
while dying?
No, please, I'm not
that great of an actor,
but I do respect my craft.
Don'tcha think?
[MILEDI gasping]
[MILEDI]
Truce?
Wait, don't!
This body is really delicate!
Calm down, please!
Deep breaths.
Let's talk this out.
Hey, look, I'm sorry, okay?
[SHEA growls]
Ha!
[HAJIME] So, the ancient power
you have is gravitic magic.
[MILEDI]
Please use it wisely.
Oh, but you and bunny girl don't
really have an affinity for it.
You'd need to be
at much higher levels!
How would you know?
Don't just assume that!
[MILEDI] Blondie here would
be perfect for it, though!
If you train hard,
you'll become a master!
Yeah, that's a good start.
But don't you have other stuff?
Like some useful artifacts or
rare materials or something?
Come on, hand them over!
Where's the stash?
I wanna be weighed
down with crap
when I get outta here.
I know you're hiding
the good stuff somewhere,
you annoying little turd.
To think that the first people
down here would be so greedy.
Yeah, I'm over this.
Later, you guys.
Don't come back.
[HAJIME]
You bastard!
[MILEDI]
Toodle‐oo!
Try not to die in
another labyrinth!
[laughing]
What're you lookin' at?
[GROUP yells]
[SHEA screams]
[HAJIME coughs]
I'm gonna come back here one
day and obliterate that idiot.
Yue, Shea, you two all right?
[YUE coughs]
Yes, I think so.
[HAJIME]
Was that...?
Hey, can't you swim?
[HAJIME]
C'mon. Wake up! Shea!
[HAJIME grunting]
[SHEA giggles]
[HAJIME gasps]
You little‐‐ Go drown
again, ya damn rabbit in heat!
That girl. Rabbit.
I can't believe she went
full tongue right after
I brought her back from
the brink of death. Moron.
[SHEA screaming]
[GIRL 07A]
Hello, travelers!
Um...
Welcome to the Masaka Inn.
I need a room now.
And food, whatever you have.
Might as well add on
a bath, too.
[SHEA] Just one room
for all three, please.
[GIRL 07A]
Wait...
The three of you
will share one bed?
No. We'll take two rooms.
Hajime and I will have our own.
Shea's alone.
Wait, that's not fair,
why am I excluded from
the group sleepover?
A single room works.
End of story.
But you'll be distracting.
Distracting?
What are you planning
to do in there?
[YUE]
What do you think?
[SHEA] New idea.
You sleep by yourself.
In another inn, for all I care.
I'll snuggle with Hajime.
Got it?
Oh, yeah? Then what?
Uh... I guess...
After that...
I'll ask Hajime to
take my virginity!
What's wrong?
Was it something I said?
[HAJIME growls]
[gunshot]
[ERI, SUZU] ARIFURETA: From
Commonplace to Worlds Strongest.