[HAJIME chewing]
[HAJIME gulping]
I guess eating this guy
isn't gonna up my level
any further.
If I can't find a way up,
then I'm just gonna
have to go down.
I can use Transmute
to move horizontally,
so it stands to reason
I should be able to use it
to move vertically, too.
This labyrinth's supposed
to have a hundred levels.
Be real nice if I
knew which one I was on.
[HAJIME]
I can't see a damn thing.
It's too dark.
Good way to get myself
killed, but I've got no choice.
[HAJIME gasps]
Crap.
Damn it.
It's been petrified.
[HAJIME chuckles]
[ELIHELD] Now, then,
tell us of your discovery.
What did you find
on the 20th level
of the Great Orcus Labyrinth?
[MELD] Your Highness,
we found a new kind of trap
that utilized a glanz crystal.
It instantly transported
us to the 65th level.
Oh? That's quite deep.
Indeed, it's the deepest level
that's ever been reached,
as well as the lair
of the Behemoth.
[MELD] I regret to report that
our fight against the Behemoth
and Traum Soldiers was both
unsuccessful and deadly.
[ISHTAR] Word that one of God's
chosen heroes has perished
is spreading throughout
the kingdom.
This isn't the outcome
we had hoped for.
You will not speak any
further about this matter.
Understood?
Sire.
[ISHTAR] That goes
for all of you, Heroes.
[SHIZUKU gasps]
[growling]
What the‐‐?
[CROWD muttering]
The Behemoth!
It sent us to the 65th floor!
This is the furthest
anyone's ever gotten.
[MELD] Take the students and
attack the Traum Soldiers!
[KNIGHT 2A]
Yes, sir!
[MELD] The rest of you,
hold this beast back!
[KOUKI]
We'll help!
[MELD]
You fools!
[SHIZUKU grunts]
[BEAST growling]
[HAJIME]
Now's your chance to escape!
[SHIZUKU]
Huh?
[MELD]
I swear we'll rescue you.
Be strong. I'll be back.
[HAJIME]
It's no good.
[MELD] Get out of there, kid!
We'll cover you!
[MELD]
Second volley! Fire!
[HAJIME]
Is that blast targeting me?
[yells]
Nagumo!
You can't!
But he's alone out there!
[KAORI gasps]
[HAJIME yelling]
[KAORI]
Nagumo!
[KOUKI]
Don't!
Let go of me! We have to
save him! He'll die!
Please, calm down!
[KOUKI]
There's nothing we can do.
I promised he would be safe...
I promised I would
protect him down here!
‐‐[SHIZUKU] It's not your fault!
‐‐[KAORI] Nagumo!
What do you think you're doing?
[SHIZUKU]
Kouki.
He did what needed to be done.
[MELD] She was going
to get herself killed.
We can't lose any more of you.
[KOUKI]
You're right.
[SHIZUKU]
Come on.
You can cut open a path for us.
Get us all out of here.
[KOUKI]
Right. I'm on it.
[ISHTAR] I bid you welcome
to the world of Tortus.
On behalf of the entire kingdom,
allow me to say
what an honor it is
to have you brave
heroes here among us.
[KOUKI] According to Pope
Ishtar, there are three races
of creatures who
inhabit this world.
They are the humans,
the demons, and the beastmen.
For centuries, human and
demon‐kind had been engaged
in a bloody war, with neither
side gaining the advantage.
But then, the demons
learned to control monsters,
tipping the scales
in their favor...
...and pushing humanity
to the brink of destruction.
To prevent humankind's fall,
Ehit, the god of
creation worshipped
by the people of Tortus,
summoned heroes
with incredible power
to this kingdom.
We are those heroes.
The people in this kingdom
are in danger of annihilation.
We can't let them die!
We were brought here to fight,
and I say that we do it!
No! Amanogawa, you can't!
I understand why
you want to help,
but please think about what
they're asking you to do.
Your lives would be in danger!
I'll fight, too.
I wouldn't want you
to have to go it all alone.
[KOUKI]
Are you sure?
Yeah, count me in.
I don't see what
other option we have.
That's great!
[KAORI]
Uh... and, um...
If Shizuku's going
to fight the demons,
then I'll try to help, too.
Thanks, Kaori!
[AIKO]
You can't do this!
I forbid it, do you hear me?
I'm your teacher,
so what I say goes.
We're going to have
these people send us home
as soon as possible.
Until that happens,
you are still my students,
and you will do as you're told.
Which means absolutely no
fighting a war against...
It doesn't make sense.
How are we suddenly so powerful?
[HIYAMA]
It's fine.
Nobody's ever gonna find out.
Nobody saw me do it.
Everything went perfectly.
It's fine.
[SHIZUKU]
Hiyama?
[HIYAMA gasps]
Yaegashi?
[gasps]
You seem nervous. What's up?
Uh, nothing's up! I'm fine.
How 'bout you?
Just getting some training in.
Gotta keep up my routine,
or I'll get rusty.
You're welcome to practice
with me if you want.
No, I'm good.
Um... See ya.
Was he always so
twitchy or is that new?
[SHIZUKU]
He was a confrontational guy,
always picking
fights with Nagumo.
Even after we wound up here.
Maybe he had a thing for Kaori?
Ridiculous.
[SHIZUKU gasps]
Kaori!
Thank goodness.
Hey, don't cry.
[SHIZUKU]
How are you feeling?
[KAORI]
I'm okay.
Just a little tired.
[SHIZUKU]
You should be well‐rested.
You've been asleep
for five days.
For five days?
What happened?
I remember we were down
in the Labyrinth, fighting,
and then‐‐
[SHIZUKU]
Hey, are you thirsty?
[KAORI]
What happened after that?
Where's Nagumo?
He's okay, isn't he?
We did save him, right?
Talk to me!
He's gone.
You're wrong!
That can't be true. No!
[SHIZUKU]
Careful!
Stop, I'm fine.
I have to go.
It's too late!
I have to!
Nagumo's waiting for
us in that Labyrinth.
Can you imagine how frightened
he must be down there
all by himself?
[KAORI crying]
[HAJIME] I've got no idea how
much farther I have to go
before I hit the
bottom of this place.
By my count, I've gone down
50 levels from where I landed.
Maybe the answers I'm looking
for are hidden behind
those doors.
It's time to open Pandora's box.
I wonder, will I find hope
waiting inside like she did?
I'm surviving this.
I'm surviving this
hellhole and going home.
Nobody's gonna stand in my way.
If they do...
...they die.
[HAJIME]
Hmm.
I've got nothing.
I studied a ton
back at the castle,
but I don't remember seeing
anything like this before.
Guess that could mean
it's really ancient.
All right.
I'll use Transmute
and see what happens.
[HAJIME grunts]
Damn it!
Of course.
I should've expected
that old cliché.
[RED CYCLOPS growls]
[HAJIME] Sorry.
I know how this plays out,
and I'm not gonna
wait around so you two
can gang up on me.
[BLUE CYCLOPS growls]
[HAJIME chuckles]
This guy's using
defensive magic, huh?
Well, good thing I
already know his weakness.
[BLUE CYCLOPS growls]
Damn. He keeps
blocking my shots.
[BLUE CYCLOPS growling]
[HAJIME]
What're you waiting for?
Come and get me.
[BLUE CYCLOPS growls]
Looks like he can't get
very far from the door.
Guess you must be guarding
something pretty special.
That true, One‐Eye?
[BLUE CYCLOPS growling]
Got ya! Nowhere to go now.
[BLUE CYCLOPS growls]
[HAJIME]
Lookin' for me?
Okay, let's find out what you
and your buddy were protecting.
[KAORI]
Shizuku.
I can't give up on Nagumo yet.
I have to believe
he's still alive.
But Kaori...
I'm not stupid.
I know that most likely
that's not the case.
But still, we won't know for
sure until we go back and check.
I'll work hard and get stronger.
I'll get stronger, then go
back and see for myself.
Shizuku...
Will you help me
find the truth?
Of course I will.
I'll be with you the
entire way, I promise.
Thank you!
Hey, you don't have to thank me.
We're friends, right?
Mana stones?
So these guys were the
keepers of the keys, then.
I'll worry about
eating them later.
For now...
What the‐‐?
[GIRL]
Who's there?
Is that... a person?
[HAJIME]
Well, gotta go.
[GIRL gasps]
Wait! Please! Help me!
[HAJIME]
Not happening.
[GIRL]
Please. I'll do anything!
Come on, you're obviously
sealed away down here
for a reason.
Only an absolute idiot
would release you.
And since I'm not
an idiot, I'll pass.
Besides, I'm busy.
No! [coughs]
You're wrong. It's not my fault.
Listen.
I'm here because I was betrayed.
Damn it.
Okay, so you were betrayed.
And whoever did the
betraying felt the need
to lock you up way down here.
Care to explain why that is?
This place is no joke.
You must have someone scared.
Hey, are you gonna answer me?
Start talking or
I'm out of here.
The truth is, I come from
a long line of vampires.
I was gifted with great power.
A gift I always used
to protect my people.
But then...
One day, my ministers
said I was no longer needed.
My uncle told me that he
would rule our people instead.
And I was fine
with that, really.
[HAJIME] So you're some
kinda royalty, then?
[GIRL] Yes, but they said
I posed too great a threat.
And since they couldn't kill me,
they sealed me down here.
So, that's why.
What do you mean,
they couldn't kill you?
I heal very quickly.
My injuries repair themselves.
[HAJIME] That the "power"
you were talking about?
That, and... I can
also manipulate mana.
Without a circle.
Seriously?
Those are some
incredible powers.
I can see why you'd
be so hard to kill.
[GIRL]
Will you help me?
[HAJIME sighs] I'm gonna
regret this later, aren't I?
This thing really
doesn't wanna let go.
But I'm not as
weak as I used to be!
[HAJIME yelling]
[HAJIME]
Come on, damn you!
[yelling]
[HAJIME]
Want some?
You're so warm.
I'm alive.
That kind of comes
with the territory.
Can I ask your name?
[HAJIME]
I'm Hajime.
Hajime Nagumo.
[GIRL]
Hajime.
Hajime. Hajime.
‐‐[GIRL] Hajime.
‐‐[HAJIME] What's yours?
[HAJIME]
You've got a name, right?
Give me one.
What? You want me
to give you one?
Did you forget
yours or something?
[GIRL] I don't need
my old name anymore.
I want one that you choose!
I don't see why you'd want‐‐
'Kay, so what?
Just come up with a random name?
Uh...
Um, how about Yue?
[YUE]
Yue?
Uh‐huh.
Where I come from, it's a
word that means "moon."
[YUE]
Moon?
[HAJIME]
When I first walked in,
this room looked
like it was filled
with stars, and your
golden hair reminded me
of the moon in the night sky.
Sound good?
Perfect.
It sounds perfect!
Ah! Thank you!
It's no problem.
[HAJIME gasps]
[HAJIME yells]
[YUE]
No! Hajime!
[KAORI]
Arifureta:
From Commonplace
to World's Strongest!