[HAJIME grunts]
[grunting]
No, Hajime!
[HAJIME grunts]
I let my guard down.
[HAJIME yells]
[YUE]
No! Hajime!
I guess that thing's
supposed to keep you in here?
Take this.
You gotta wear something.
Don't look at me like that.
Hold on to me and
don't let go, okay?
All right, ugly!
Better stay outta my way,
or you're gonna be my dinner!
[HAJIME]
Tch!
[HAJIME grunts]
[HAJIME chuckles]
[HAJIME]
Quick step!
[HAJIME growls]
I've gotta crack that shell
if I'm gonna take this
thing down.
[HAJIME]
What are you doing?
[HAJIME gasps]
[HAJIME grunts]
[HAJIME growls]
So it can control the
ground around itself?
Nice trick.
But it happens to be
my specialty too!
That was delicious.
Azure Blaze!
[BEAST shrieks]
[BEAST growling]
Hey, you don't look so hot.
[YUE] Those high‐level
spells are tiring.
[BEAST shrieks]
I know this is
asking a lot of you.
And I'm sorry.
But do you think you
can cast it again?
I can, but it won't
be nearly as strong.
That works for me.
Now, then.
You remember the spot where
I shot him with my Donner?
[YUE]
Mm‐hmm.
When I give the
signal, you hit him
in the exact same place.
Okay, let's do this!
Yue!
[YUE gasps]
[HAJIME growls]
[BEAST shrieks]
[YUE]
Why?
[HAJIME]
Huh?
Why didn't you just leave
me behind and run away?
[HAJIME]
That's not how I do things.
You were betrayed by the
people you put your trust in.
And I promised that
I would keep you safe.
I won't leave unless
you're with me.
[HAJIME]
If I remember right,
300 years ago,
the vampires were supposedly
eradicated in a war.
Has it been that long?
[HAJIME] That must've started
after you were sealed.
Wait, exactly how old
does that make you?
Uh...
Don't be rude.
[HAJIME chuckles]
So, what's the deal?
Do all vampires live that long?
[YUE]
No, I'm the exception.
I don't age because
I can regenerate.
[HAJIME] Huh. Your special
magic makes you immortal.
[YUE]
Mm‐hmm.
Got it.
I don't suppose you'd
happen to know where we are
right now.
Or, better yet, a quick
way to the surface.
[YUE]
No, I don't.
But legends say this labyrinth
was built by one
of the Mavericks.
What's a Maverick?
They were once
messengers of the gods.
But then they rebelled.
And turned against
their masters.
They actually tried to
put up a fight against gods?
In doing so, they attempted
to destroy our whole world.
But their plans crumbled.
After their failure, the
Mavericks fled to the safety
of their labyrinths.
[HAJIME] And you think
we're currently sitting
in one of them.
It's said that they're still
stalking in the darkness.
Hiding in the deepest
depths of their new homes.
So that's what's waiting
in the last ring of hell.
[YUE] If we go there, we might
find a way to the surface.
Possibly, yeah.
If someone could
wield divine magic,
I'm betting they could
conjure up a path to the surface
without any problem.
The monster's carapace
is Shtar ore,
a stone with a unique
magical property.
The more mana it absorbs,
the stronger it becomes.
No wonder it was
so hard to kill.
What is that you're making?
It's a weapon.
An antimaterial rifle
meets a railgun.
Railgun?
Exactly. You saw my revolver.
Donner is a powerful gun.
The bullets are special, too.
But I'm gonna use this
Shtar ore to upgrade it
into something that
packs a bigger punch.
All done. Let's see now.
This one's named Schlagen.
How did you come to
be down here, Hajime?
And how is it you can
directly manipulate mana?
[HAJIME]
Huh?
Why are you able
to digest monsters?
Are you a human?
What happened to your arm?
Hey, one question at a time!
I'll explain everything,
just gimme a sec!
[HAJIME]
Let's see.
Where's the best place
to start the story?
One day, my classmates
and I were summoned
to this world by the god Ehit.
The people here said
we were supposed to be
the ones who'd save
humanity from demonkind.
I was assigned
to be a Synergist,
which isn't really a combat job.
Everyone said I was
totally useless in a fight.
Which seemed true.
We teamed up with the
Royal Guard to clear out
this labyrinth,
but things went wrong.
In the middle of
fighting a Behemoth,
one of my classmates
betrayed me and I ended up
in the depths.
A huge beast ate my arm,
almost killing me.
But I decided that I was going
to survive no matter what.
That meant using my Synergist
abilities to kill a monster
and eat it.
[YUE crying]
Whoa, why're you crying?
It's just... so sad.
You've suffered just like me.
You shouldn't be sad.
I don't give a crap about
my classmates anymore.
I don't even want revenge
for what happened.
All I care about
is getting as
strong as possible.
I have to do my all to survive
so that I can find
a way back home.
Back home?
[HAJIME]
Yeah, that's the plan.
I mean, sure, a lot
has changed about me.
But getting back home
is still my ultimate goal.
Oh. I'd say the same.
But I have no home now.
I don't need my old name.
I want one that you choose!
[HAJIME]
Ah, man.
[HAJIME] How about you
come with me, then?
Back to my home, I mean.
It might be pretty boring.
The world I come from
doesn't have any magic in it.
But we can figure something out.
Whaddaya think?
You don't have to.
It's totally your choice.
Sound good?
[YUE]
You're sure?
[rumbling]
[KOUKI]
Status, open!
[MELD]
Kouki Amanogawa. Job, hero.
Hmph. It appears that you've
grown even stronger.
We'll continue training
in the labyrinth.
But with only the teammates
who are present right now.
I trust you will
prepare accordingly.
Yes, sir!
That is all.
Failure's not an option. Right?
[KOUKI]
Come on, guys.
We're gonna make sure
to boost our levels!
Yeah!
[HAJIME]
Not cool!
Keep it up, Hajime.
You are way too calm right now!
What the hell are these dinos?
No matter how many
of 'em I slaughter,
they just keep coming!
Actually, there
might be even more.
How's that possible?
Not to mention,
there're flowers growing
outta their heads!
[YUE giggles]
I think they're kinda cute.
Are you kidding me?!
And why was the one
earlier trampling them?
[HAJIME] Wait. Maybe those
flowers are like parasites.
Could be.
Well, if that is the case...
Then something
is controlling them?
Think so.
Which means if we
don't kill whatever it is
that's ordering
the flowers around,
we'll have to battle every
monster on this level.
[HAJIME sighs]
[HAJIME]
Where is it?
What's controlling the flowers?
Really? Hey,
little vampire princess?
You think you could
gimme a break and stop
snacking on me for a minute?
I can't help it.
Come on!
You can't still be that tired.
[HAJIME]
Now that looks suspicious.
[DINOS growling]
[HAJIME growls]
Made it. No way they're
getting through that.
You did a good job.
If you wanna repay me,
you'll stop making me carry you.
[YUE sighs]
I guess that's fair.
[HAJIME]
Now, then.
They seemed pretty desperate
to keep us outta here,
so I bet we hit the jackpot.
Don't let your guard down.
[HAJIME]
Hmm...
My Sense Presence skill
hasn't detected anything yet.
[YUE gasps]
Dammit!
Watch out. This might be
an attack from the source.
Got any idea where it could be?
Yue?
[YUE]
Hajime... Run!
Did one of those floating
green balls touch you?
[HAJIME grunts]
[yells]
[PLANT MONSTER 3A croaks]
[HAJIME grunting]
You're actually not half bad.
[PLANT MONSTER 3A croaks]
Sorry, Hajime.
I can't stop!
[HAJIME grunts]
[PLANT MONSTER 3A croaks]
[HAJIME chuckles]
[laughing]
Is that it?
[PLANT MONSTER 3A croaks]
[HAJIME] I gained resistance
from tricks like that
by eating those monsters.
[YUE]
Please, no!
[HAJIME grunts]
Dammit.
[YUE]
Move!
Hajime, don't worry about me.
Just shoot!
Yue.
[PLANT MONSTER 3A croaks]
Take the shot. Do it!
Seriously?
That makes everything easier!
[YUE gasps]
[PLANT MONSTER 3A screeches]
How 'bout I rearrange
that ugly mug?
[PLANT MONSTER 3A screeches]
Hey. You all right?
Lemme know if
you still feel off.
You shot.
Uh... Yeah, because you
gave me permission.
You didn't even hesitate.
Because I wanted to take
that monster out immediately.
I knew I'd hit my mark,
but, you know.
[YUE]
I know what?
If I fired without
getting the okay,
you probably would
have been mad at me.
So, I had to wait for it.
I think you burned off
part of my scalp. Bully.
[HAJIME] It's just gonna
grow right back, though.
No biggie.
Here, this is for you.
[YUE]
I don't need it.
Oh, sure, I guess a vampire
who was sealed away
for 300 years wouldn't.
Don't you ever
feel hungry though?
[YUE]
I was before, but I'm fine now.
Did you eat something?
I must've missed that somehow.
[YUE]
I drank your blood.
Oh, whoa.
So if you have blood,
then you don't have to consume
anything else to survive?
[YUE] I could get nutrients
from normal food.
But blood is the more
effective way for me to feed.
Interesting.
[HAJIME]
Uh...
[HAJIME] Um...
Why're you licking your lips?
[YUE]
You taste good... Hajime.
[HAJIME]
Uh...!
Your blood is so rich.
[HAJIME]
Wait. Hold on a second.
No, no, no, no, no!
[yells]
[YUE]
There's no getting away.
It's time to eat.
[HAJIME] We must be getting
close to the hundredth floor.
[YUE] Feels like you're being
more careful than usual.
[HAJIME]
Yeah. We're in deep.
And the monsters have
been getting stronger
as we've descended.
I figure there might
be some kinda big boss
waiting down here for us.
What's a boss?
[HAJIME]
I'm just trying to be safe.
[HAJIME] If there's something
here, it's behind these doors.
Are you scared?
[YUE]
No. Not as long as I'm with you.
[HAJIME]
That's what a like to hear.
[SHIZUKU]
Arifureta:
From Commonplace
to World's Strongest.