[HAJIME]
Take the lead, Endo.
I haven't seen this part
of the labyrinth before.
[ENDO]
Right! Got it!
[ENDO] He took that Behemoth
down with one shot.
There's never a shortcut
when you need one.
We must hurry if we
are to arrive in time to help.
Right about here, then?
Catch your breath
for a sec, Endo.
[ENDO]
What's up?
Guess you could say
we found a shortcut.
[MYU grunts]
[ENDO]
Huh?
What's that?
[HAJIME]
I call it the Pile Bunker.
It's a pile driver that
uses electromagnetic force
and explosives to punch
through just about anything.
[ENDO]
Wait. For real?
[HAJIME]
Yep.
The rods are made from ore I
compressed using Transmute.
Coat them with azantium, the
strongest metal in the world,
and you've got something
that's basically unbreakable.
[ENDO grunts]
‐‐[HAJIME] Endo.
‐‐[ENDO] Huh?
I'm gonna head down now.
You can follow
whenever you're ready.
[ENDO]
A hole?
Oh, come on, you've
gotta be kidding me!
[yells]
This is crazy!
[HAJIME]
Hmph.
I see you two are
still good friends.
Good for you.
That's Hajime!
Wait, you can't be serious!
Uh... Hold on.
I don't understand how...
This is just insane!
I can't believe you're
standing there.
No, really!
What the hell is going on?
[HAJIME]
Damn, calm down.
You're supposed to be
the cool and collected one.
Remember?
[SHEA chuckles]
[ENDO yelling]
Hey, guys!
I brought us some help
from the surface.
It's Endo!
[BEASTS growling]
Yue. You're on guard duty.
Keep the others safe.
Right.
Shea, you get over there and
check on those fallen knights.
I'm all over it!
[ENDO yelps]
Tio and Myu,
take out the weaklings.
Of course, Master.
Yeah, that sounds fun!
[HAJIME]
Okay, then.
[KAORI]
Hajime!
[HAJIME]
I got this, just sit tight.
[TIO] Please allow us
to handle these beasts.
We're strong!
[SHIZUKU, KAORI]
Huh?
Pretty bold of you to split
your party before you know
what you're up against.
[HAJIME] If you don't feel
like dyin', then you're free
to leave.
[CATOREA]
What?
[HAJIME] I'm just giving you
a chance to run away
before I kill you.
How dare you.
I'll make you regret
those foolish words
when you die by my hand.
If you wanna be my enemy,
I'm gonna have
to rescind my offer.
[KAORI]
Look out!
Okay, I'll bite.
What the hell is this
half‐assed magic of yours?
It's a neat party trick.
[HIYAMA]
No freakin' way.
[growling]
How could you possibly
have known where they were?
[HAJIME grunts]
[MONSTERS growl]
[MONSTER growls]
[CATOREA grunts]
He can't be this strong.
Quick. I need healing.
[gasps] When did he...?
He targeted the healer
without her noticing.
[HAJIME grunting]
You know, it seems to me
like you were the one
who didn't know what
they were up against.
Who is this guy?
I know it's hard to believe,
but that's Nagumo.
[KOUKI]
What?
[RYUTARO, KOUKI]
Huh?
Like I said,
it's hard to believe!
But this is the same guy who
fell off the bridge that day.
There's no way.
I do find that hard to believe.
I mean, it doesn't make
a lot of sense to me either,
but that doesn't
change the facts.
[HIYAMA]
It's not him!
[grunts]
Quit makin' shit up, Endo!
Nagumo's dead!
We all saw it happen!
I checked his status
plate to be sure,
and there's no doubt
about it‐‐that's him!
Then there's only
one explanation!
He forged the plate and
he's plotting something.
We can't trust this guy!
[YUE]
You're so loud.
[YUE] You're not planning to
get in his way again, are you?
[RYUTARO]
Here they come!
[MONSTERS growl]
Hey, wait, don't push yourself!
[ERI]
Suzu?
I... I have to fight.
I'll protect you!
Just leave it to me.
Dark Firmament, rise.
[MONSTERS growling]
[SHEA yells]
[SHEA grunting]
Gotcha!
Don't celebrate yet.
[CATOREA]
You haven't won.
Yaegashi, use this!
‐‐Sorry!
‐‐[KAORI yelps]
[SHIZUKU]
It's so light.
And incredibly sharp.
What the hell are you?
[HAJIME]
Is that all you got?
[CATOREA chuckles]
Crashing Gaol!
[KAORI gasps]
Oh, no! Nagumo!
[GROUP gasps]
This is bad.
Papa, no!
Pa... pa?
[CATOREA grunts]
So this is the end, then?
[HAJIME]
Sounds about right.
[CATOREA] My high‐level magic
meant absolutely nothing to you.
Are you sure you're
really human?
I definitely used to be,
but not anymore.
You're some kind of monster.
Kaori, that kind of hurts.
[KAORI]
She called him Papa, didn't she?
Didn't she?
[SHIZUKU]
Kaori?!
[HAJIME]
Right, then.
I'm not really interested in the
sentimentality of last words.
So how about this.
You tell me how
a demon like yourself
got ahold of all these monsters.
Then you can tell me what the
hell you're doing down here.
Those can be your last words.
Gimme one good reason
I should talk to you.
[gunshots]
[CATOREA yells]
[GROUP gasps]
[HAJIME] Well, let me
tell you what I think.
I think those monsters of
yours were created
by a form of ancient magic.
And there's only one
way to gain the ability
to use ancient magic
as far as I'm aware,
so I bet you demons
cleared a great labyrinth.
Looks like I'm
right on the money.
Tell me.
Did you really think
you were strong enough
to make it to the end of hell?
It's starting to make sense.
If you were anything like them,
then your monstrous
appearance and inhuman strength
would check out.
[HAJIME]
"Anything like them," huh?
So the monsters were
given to you by the person
who actually did the dirty work.
Well, that answers
all my questions.
[CATOREA] If we're done here,
then shut the hell up
and end this already.
Thought you'd never ask.
One more thing before I die.
My lover will hunt you
down and kill you
for what you've done today.
Heh.
Demon or god, I don't care.
I'll kill anyone who
comes after me.
But hey.
If your lover's just
a puppet like you are,
they won't be able to touch me.
Nagumo, don't do it!
It's over, she can't
fight us anymore.
You don't have to kill‐‐
[gunshot]
[KOUKI]
Why?
[HIYAMA gasps]
[KOUKI]
Nagumo!
[HAJIME] Shea.
How's Captain Meld doing?
[SHEA]
If we'd gotten here any later,
we wouldn't have been
able to save him.
I gave him the
Holy Water like you said,
but are you sure that was okay?
It's so rare.
Yeah. He's been a big help.
So I'm not gonna let him
die on my watch.
Hajime.
Oh, hey, Yue.
Thanks a lot.
I couldn't have
done it without you.
[SHEA]
Oh, come on!
Everyone is coming over to
check on their injured friend.
Maybe learn to read
the room a little bit.
I did what I could
for Captain Meld,
but I didn't have
the mana to heal him.
We gave him some Holy Water,
so after a little rest,
he'll be fine.
Oh, thank God.
I thought for sure
we would lose him.
[KAORI]
I thought we'd lost you too.
I'm so glad you're alive.
I missed you.
I couldn't protect
you back then.
I'm sorry.
[crying]
It seems like I
had you pretty worried.
But, uh...
I clearly didn't die
and I'm here now.
So there's no need to apologize.
Or to cry.
Oh, come on.
[KAORI crying]
Don't cry, okay?
I missed you so much!
[crying]
[SHIZUKU] Hug her right now,
you heartless bastard!
[crying continues]
Oh, I see.
It's been too long since
he's ignored me like this.
[KOUKI]
Why did you have to kill her?
She wasn't even putting
up a fight anymore!
[HAJIME] Ugh, you're
like a broken record.
Listen.
I know you think you're
mad about me killing her,
but let me give you
my take on it.
I think you're actually
mad at yourself
for being unable to do
what needed to be done.
Stop projecting your
weaknesses onto me.
That's not what I'm doing.
I'm only saying what anyone
else would be saying
if they were in my position.
It's always been kill
or be killed in this world,
and I'd rather be the
one doing the killing.
You got a problem with that?
Yeah, of course I have
a problem with murder!
I kill anyone who
makes me their enemy.
Anyone who stands in my way.
I don't show mercy.
And I don't discriminate.
[HAJIME] I don't care
if we were classmates.
I won't hesitate to kill you.
[KOUKI]
You...
But don't get the wrong idea.
I don't think of us
as classmates or friends
or comrades.
I came here because
I owed Shirasaki a favor.
Once I'm gone, I'm gone forever.
He's different.
He's changed so much.
[KAORI]
You think so, huh?
[MYU] Papa, I'm hungry.
Can we get something to eat?
[HAJIME] We sure can, Princess,
we'll get whatever you want.
We'll find something yummy.
[MYU]
Yay! [laughs]
[HAJIME]
What the hell?!
Oh... Um, so...
We gathered a force to
help you guys in there.
We never expected it
to be over so quickly.
And the contents
of Ilwer's letter
were so unbelievable,
we just... Oh, boy.
The heroes have
returned unscathed!
Battalion dismissed!
[SOLDIERS cheering]
[KAORI]
This is who Hajime is now.
But has he really changed?
[KAORI]
Okay.
Uh, what's up?
Wish me luck.
I'm gonna do it now.
Good luck.
[KAORI]
Hajime.
I was...
I was wondering if you
would let me come with you.
I mean, I'm coming with you!
Huh?
You don't have what
it takes to join us.
What do you mean
"what it takes"?
Are you trying to say I don't
care enough about Hajime?
I bet I care about him
more than you.
[TIO]
Ooh! A contest of wills.
I love you, Hajime.
Shirasaki.
I'm afraid I have feelings
for another woman.
I can't reciprocate yours.
[KAORI]
It's Yue, isn't it?
[HAJIME]
Yeah, so, uh...
I'm still coming with you!
I know you can't love me yet.
But one day,
you will see me that way.
After all,
there's no one in any
world who loves you
as much as I do.
‐‐[HAJIME] I, uh...
‐‐[YUE] Come with us, then.
Please allow me to show
you how wrong you are.
I'm looking forward
to defeating you.
I accept your challenge.
Let's have a fair fight.
Okay, Kaori?
Don't cry when you
lose to me, all right?
I think my eyes must be
playing tricks on me.
I could swear that
I see a thunder cloud
and a lightning dragon
forming behind Yue!
[MYU] And I see a big,
smiling, white face
floating behind Miss Kaori!
[TIO]
Look at the two of them.
This will be quite an
interesting journey.
[KAORI gasps]
[HAJIME yelps]
By the way, I've been
meaning to ask you
about this "Papa" business!
Is this girl really your
daughter, Hajime?
[HAJIME]
Shirasaki‐‐
[KAORI]
So, who's the mother, big shot?
Yue? Shea?
Don't tell me it
was that pervert!
[SHIZUKU]
Kaori, calm down!
[SHIZUKU, KAORI grunt]
[KAORI] She better be
the only one! Is she?
[HAJIME] Is it really okay
to bring her with us?
I mean...
It'll be fine.
We're the world's
strongest, right?
[MYU laughs]
Shirasaki!
We're leaving early
tomorrow morning!
Don't be late.
[SOLDIERS cheering]
[SHIZUKU]
Hey, Nagumo.
Thanks for letting me use this.
You can keep it if you want.
I'm not really much
of a sword guy.
Well, thank you then.
[HAJIME] I made it by condensing
the world's strongest metal.
You'll never find a
sharper, more durable sword.
Wow. That's an incredible
skill you have.
I always thought a synergist
would be useless in battle.
But, hey, you've
proven me wrong.
About a lot of things.
I'll use this sword
as if it were a part
of my own body.
[YUE] I see.
She's the real final boss.
Huh? You really think so?
[SHIZUKU]
Huh?
What are you guys doing here?!
This isn't what you
think, I swear.
I'm just thanking her!
[SHIZUKU] Why're you
looking at me like that?
Seriously, stop!
[KOUKI]
Kaori!
Shizuku.
You're not going
to say anything?
[SHIZUKU]
What do you want me to say?
[KOUKI] How long have you
known she felt this way?
Oh, I've known for a long time.
Kaori's always held
a candle for Nagumo.
I wish that I'd known sooner.
You're not going to
leave too, are you?
[SHIZUKU]
Who knows?
I'm going to miss you.
[SUZU] Good luck out there,
and remember,
we've always got your
back, no matter what!
[ERI]
Take care of yourself!
I will, don't worry.
Thank you.
Off you go.
You've waited long
enough for this.
Goodbye, Shizuku.
Whoa, what is that?
I've never seen
anything like it!
I'm pretty sure it's an SUV.
[KAORI]
Um, Hajime...
Why are we all crammed
in the back like this?
This is how it is.
Yue sits up front while
the rest of us fight
for leg‐room in the back.
But one day, it'll be me
who sits in the coveted
front seat!
Tio, doesn't this seating
arrangement bother you at all?
It's funny you
should mention that.
Oh, it bothers me so
much more than you
could possibly imagine,
but not in the way
that you think!
[chuckling]
Oh, wow, you really
are a pervert, huh?
Sexy neglecting!
What the‐‐?
Where the hell did you
learn those words, Myu?
[MYU]
Papa. I'm hungry!
[SHEA]
Ooh! I'm hungry, too!
[TIO]
As am I.
[HAJIME]
I swear, you guys!
[KAORI]
Watch where you're going!
I could eat.
[KAORI]
Wait. What?
No, hold on!
Really, why did she
just lick her lips?
[HAJIME] I'm going to find
a way home and take Yue
and the others with me.
Anyone who tries to
stop me or gets in my way
is my enemy.
And I kill my enemies.
Men. Demons.
Even if they happen to be gods.