Head of the Fuhren
Adventurer's Guild.
Ilwer Chang.
It's nice to meet you.
Hajime, Yue, and Shea.
You're not an easy
group to track down.
I've heard some
interesting rumors.
The people of Brooke
are all talking about a trio
of powerful travelers who carved
a path through Reisen Gorge.
Ya got the wrong group.
Local legends or not, I can
tell you've got the skills
to handle the request
I would like to make of you.
Don't think so.
Look, do you mind if I
just tell you what it is?
It's a lot less paperwork
for me if I can say
I formally asked for your help.
Tch. Just as I expected
from the head of a guild.
You won't take no for an answer.
She was unusually quiet.
Turns out she's asleep.
Well we're not
stopping on the way,
so let her rest while
she still can.
You're asking me to track
down a missing party?
[ILWER]
Correct.
A party of adventurers was
headed into the northern
mountains on a survey.
Count Cudeta's third son
was traveling with them.
I want you three to
rescue Will Cudeta.
A Count's son, huh?
He must've been traveling with
some pretty heavy muscle then.
[ILWER]
That's the troubling part.
Their disappearance might
mean they encountered
something stronger
than themselves.
And, if that's the case,
then a lot of people
are going to get hurt.
We know nothing of their fate,
and nothing of the enemy.
The Count is a friend of mine,
and he's turned to me for help.
[HAJIME]
A friend, huh?
Will your group agree
to take on this request?
Absolutely not.
Now, if there's nothing else,
I think we'd better go.
I'll make sure you're well
rewarded for your efforts.
[HAJIME] Sorry, but we're
in a bit of a hurry.
Well, then.
How about I simply agree
to always look the other way
when you find yourself
bumping up against
the rules of the
Adventurer's Guild?
I'll admit it's becoming
quite a tantalizing offer.
But I do have two conditions.
And they are?
[HAJIME]
First,
the three of us are going
to need you to make us
some Status Plates.
[ILWER]
And the second?
If we ever need you, you agree
to do exactly as we say.
Very well.
I think we have a deal.
Smart man.
Hajime.
You were so forceful.
Yeah, I was.
He clearly had his back
against the wall.
The more something
means to someone
the more you can get them
to agree to do for you.
There's something
more to it, though.
You figure it out?
Right now, we're headed to Ur.
We'll get some food and spend
the night in the continent's
largest rice farming
area before we go up
to the mountains to look
for that lost party.
Rice farming?
I'm so excited!
I haven't had any rice
since I came to this world.
It's been so long, it's weird
to think I used to eat it
every day.
In that case...
I can't wait to have some.
[AIKO] Good job out
there today, everyone!
Fill your bellies and get ready
to work hard again tomorrow!
‐‐Right!
[GROUP]
Let's dig in!
[sighs]
Are you feeling okay?
You're not thinking about
Shimizu again, are you?
[AIKO]
Where could he have gone?
It's been a whole week now.
It just doesn't seem right.
Nothing like this has ever
happened with him before.
I should've been keeping
a closer eye on him.
Don't worry. I'm sure he's fine.
Absolutely!
He'll be back before we know it.
Thank you!
You're right, worrying about him
isn't going to solve anything.
[YUUKA]
Heh.
[OWNER 08A] I hope you're
enjoying the food this evening.
How is the meal?
Everything's delicious,
as always!
Good, I needed to
hear that tonight.
Hm? Is something wrong?
[OWNER 08A] Unfortunately,
and I hate to disappoint you,
but the last of our
spices were used during
today's dinner prep.
Huh? How did a restaurant
come to run out of spices,
if you don't mind my asking?
[OWNER 08A] It sounds like
there's some serious trouble
up in the mountains, and it's
cut the spice traders off
from their usual route.
What trouble?
[OWNER 08A] Rumors say a gang
of monsters suddenly appeared.
And just the other day,
a group of high‐ranking
adventurers made their way
out there and didn't come back.
[AIKO] That's more than
a little concerning.
But thankfully,
Somebody else has been sent
here to deal with the problem.
A group of guests
checked in today saying
that they had been asked to
search for the missing party
by the head of the Fuhren
Adventurer's Guild himself.
Oh?
Well, whoever they are,
they must be pretty tough.
[SHEA] How many times
do I have to ask you?
Will you stop excluding
me to retreat into
your own little world?
Do you even hear me, Hajime?
[HAJIME]
Yeah, I hear you.
I just don't wanna see you.
So... Separate rooms.
[SHEA] Aww!
Yue, are you listening to this?
He's being so mean to me! Help!
[YUE]
Bad boy, Hajime.
[HAJIME]
Yeah, yeah.
Did they say what I
thought they just said?
Yeah, and his voice
sounds familiar!
Am I wrong here?
Nagumo?
Uh... Ms. Aiko?
[gasps]
It is you.
It really is you, isn't it?
I'm so... I'm so glad
you're alive!
Nope, you got the wrong guy.
‐‐Huh?
‐‐Bye.
Wait! Hold on, please.
You may look a little
different than you used to,
but there's no hiding
the fact that you just
said my name!
No. You heard me wrong.
It's, uh...
Oh, right!
It's a regional word
that means "tiny woman!"
Yeah!
[AIKO] Then you were just
being incredibly rude?
Nice try, but no one is that
mean to a stranger immediately!
You can't trick me!
I'm a teacher!
Please!
What happened to you?
Why do you look like that?
Why haven't you come
back to everyone?
Answer me!
Nagumo!
[YUE]
Leave him alone.
You're clearly bothering him.
And just who are you?
Can't you see I'm trying
to have a heartfelt reunion
with one of my students?
Oh?
Looks like you're
throwing a fit.
[AIKO gasps]
I lost my composure.
Let's try this again.
You are Nagumo, right?
[HAJIME sighs]
Yeah.
So how ya doin'?
Been a while.
Hajime.
You can't just ignore her.
Check it out.
They have curry here.
Oh, you don't know what that is.
Well, trust me.
It's a little spicy, but I'm
confident you're gonna like it.
I do. I trust you
with all my heart.
If you think I'll like it,
that's what I want.
How long did you practice that?
It was so smooth.
Nice work.
Excuse me, we're ready to order.
[AIKO]
I think I've waited long enough.
You can order your food after
you've answered my questions.
First of all, who are
these young ladies
you've been ignoring
me to talk to?
If I'm about to answer
a bunch of questions,
then at least let
me eat while I talk.
And they can speak
for themselves.
I'm Yue.
I'm Shea!
‐‐And we both belong to Hajime.
‐‐I belong to Hajime.
[AIKO gasps]
Huh? "Belong to"?
Uh... Let's get
one thing straight.
You do not belong to me.
How could you possibly
say something like that?
You stole my first kiss,
don't you remember?
We must've been over
this a dozen times now.
Mouth to mouth and
kissing aren't the sa‐‐
[AIKO]
How dare you.
Oh, yeah. You're here.
You stole that girl's first kiss
and now you're two‐timing her?
I will not let this go.
It's so reprehensible,
I almost can't believe it!
Well...
There's only one thing to do
when a student misbehaves.
Lecture time!
You've got a lot to learn!
[AIKO] Infidelity aside, I'm
glad to know you're all right.
But what happened after
you fell in the labyrinth?
I worked real hard.
[AIKO] Uh... why is your hair
white now instead of brown?
[HAJIME]
'Cause I worked real hard.
[AIKO] And how did you lose your
right eye and your left arm?
[HAJIME] I worked so hard
the darn things just fell off.
[AIKO] Why didn't you come back
or try to get in touch with us?
[HAJIME]
Didn't really have a reason to.
Take this seriously!
[SHEA gasps]
[HAJIME]
We're eating here.
Mind your manners.
Mind my manners?
The nerve!
Is that how you talk
to your superiors?
You should learn how to
conduct yourself properly.
And I will not be lectured
on table etiquette
by someone who shares their
meals with a beastman.
She might be marginally
more acceptable
if I cut those
disgusting ears off.
Or maybe not.
But it wouldn't be too
difficult to find out for sure.
[SHEA whimpers]
What's that look for?
Disrespectful worm!
How dare you show such
insolence in the face
of a templar knight!
Small men are so loud.
[DAVID gasps]
Damned heretic!
[DAVID grunts]
[GUARDS gasp]
[DAVID groans]
So then.
You gonna mind
those manners now?
[HAJIME] You won't be
getting another warning.
[YUUKA gasps]
It'll be okay. Stay calm.
[YUUKA]
Huh? Nagumo?
[HAJIME]
Now's your chance to run!
[YUUKA]
Uh... right!
[KNIGHT 08A]
I've got it from here.
Retreat to safety!
[HAJIME]
Got it!
[growling]
[NANA]
Yuuka? You okay?
I'm fine.
Just having some
trouble processing.
I'm right there with you.
It's pretty hard to believe.
I mean, look at him.
He's like an entirely
different person!
He's so...
Jeez, what's the word?
I got it.
He's wild.
And popular, too, it turns out.
[YUUKA chuckles]
That was good.
Do me a favor and
forget you ever saw me.
I forgot about you guys
a long time ago.
I'm not gonna tell you
what happened to me,
or where I've been,
or what I'm up to these days.
Go where you want, do what
you want, I don't care.
But you had better
stay out of my way.
'Cause he wasted your
only warning shot.
If any of you piss me
off again, you're dead.
Hey, Shea.
Are you still worried about
what that guy said before?
No. I'm not.
That's just the way
things are in this world.
Idiots like him are
everywhere you look.
I know, okay?
But it never gets any easier.
And that was a new one.
I didn't know that humans think
my ears are so disgusting.
They're fluffy and cute.
He was saying that to hurt you.
You like my ears?
Hajime.
Tell me what you think
about my bunny ears.
Aren't they the best?
Don't you just love them?
They're okay, I guess.
[SHEA groans]
He likes them quite a bit.
Or at least it would seem so.
He pets them while
you're sleeping.
You promised me
you wouldn't tell her!
[SHEA]
I knew it!
You do like my bunny ears,
don't try to deny it!
[HAJIME] You've got it all
wrong, I wasn't petting them,
I was, uh...
[ATSUSHI] Till now I was
scared to death of this guy.
Now I think I'm just jealous.
[HAJIME]
Later, Ms. Aiko.
[AIKO] Nagumo, don't
walk out that door!
I'm not giving up on you!
No. I refuse to stay
out of your way.
I promise I'm going to bring you
back home with everyone else!
He's gone.
And I never got to thank him.
[AIKO]
Nagumo is still alive.
But he has an absolutely
terrible attitude now.
He's probably endured a
lot since we last saw him.
But that doesn't
excuse his behavior!
I don't care,
I'm still bringing him home!
I think I should
have a say in that.
Don't you?
[AIKO gasps]
Nagumo?
How did you get in?
I find that a door is often
the best way to enter a room.
Huh? But I locked it.
Most locks are no
match for me these days.
This one would've been a snap
for any Synergist, though.
Why are you bragging?
Do you think breaking
into a woman's bedroom
is some kind of accomplishment?
What are you doing here?
Sorry, sorry.
I came to tell you something I
didn't want the others to hear.
[AIKO]
What did you want to discuss?
You're in for a wild ride.
I'm here to tell you
the history of this world
as I've come to understand it.
And after that,
I'll tell you why I'm not
coming with you.
[HAJIME] Just after the
ancient Age of Gods,
the world was plagued by war.
Humans, demons, and the
countless forms of beastman
fought ceaselessly
against each other.
Blood flowed freely.
During those centuries
of war, a group of people
who wanted to stop
it came forward.
The leader of that
group learned something
important about
their god's plan:
He didn't have one.
He was just using his
creations as pawns
in a game of war
for his own amusement.
While this god lurked
in the shadows,
pulling the strings
to cause conflict,
heroes came forth, united
in their desire to stop him.
Around that time, they
started calling themselves
"The Liberators."
But their plans fell apart
before they could do any
actual liberating.
Their god declared them
blasphemers, heretics,
enemies of the Church, hell‐bent
on destroying the world,
and turned all of
humanity against them.
The Liberators,
unable to fight the people
they had sworn to protect,
were re‐labeled "Mavericks,"
hunted down,
and taken out one by one.
But a few members did survive.
They got together
and made a new plan.
There was nothing they could
do with their limited power,
so they abandoned the idea of
attacking their god directly.
Instead, they scattered
and built great labyrinths
so they could hide from
a world that didn't
understand them.
In these labyrinths,
they prepared trials.
Whoever overcomes those
trials is granted the powers
of the Maverick
who designed them.
If someone got strong
enough in this way,
they could end this god's
sick game once and for all.
That's what I learned at
the bottom of the abyss.
And that's just about
everything I've got.
Up to you whether
or not you believe me.
I know firsthand it can
be a lot to take in.
So, any questions?
Are you saying that
you're gonna be the one
to do something about
this evil god?
Hell no.
I don't give a damn what
happens to this stupid world.
I'm just using the Mavericks
to find a solid way home.
The labyrinths are the key.
You can come with us,
if you want.
But I have a pretty strong
feeling you wouldn't last long
out there.
[AIKO] Shirasaki never gave
up on you, you know.
She wasn't going to
believe you were dead
unless she saw it
with her own eyes.
Has she been doin' okay?
Well, she sent me a letter.
She's training and growing
stronger and stronger
with the others by working
through the labyrinth together.
[HAJIME] Then you should
tell her something.
There's more to worry about
down there than just monsters.
She should keep a close eye
on her teammates as well.
[AIKO gasps]
[HAJIME] Based on your
reaction, I'm guessing you
and the others haven't
figured it out.
So I'll be perfectly clear.
You think my fall was
an accident, don't you?
[AIKO]
Yes.
One of the magic spells lost
control and happened to hit you.
[HAJIME]
Lost control, huh?
So that's what you've
told yourselves.
Unfortunately,
that isn't the case.
The one who cast
that spell hit exactly
what they were aiming for.
What do you mean?
[HAJIME]
Well...
One of your diligent students
tried real hard to kill me.
So maybe tell Shirasaki
and the others
to watch their backs
and start thinking about
who their friends are.
[door closes]
It... can't be.
[sighs] I think I know
where this is headed.
Go on, let's hear it.
We're going to help
you in the mountains.
A search party should be
as big as possible to cover
more ground, wouldn't you agree?
No, thanks.
I told you to stay
out of my way.
And to be totally honest...
There's no chance any of
you could keep up with us.
Okay, I know you're strong,
but you're not saying
that you can run faster
than our horses, are you?
[HAJIME sighs]
[GROUP gasps]
[HAJIME]
Do you get it now?
Okay, bye.
Out of the way, please.
Don't wanna get blood on it.
[AIKO]
Hold on a second!
Please let us come.
You laid out some pretty
serious history last night
and I want to talk
about it some more.
We could talk on the road,
or while we're searching,
it doesn't matter to me.
In exchange.
I promise to
leave you alone.
We'll part ways and I won't
drag you back with us.
[sighs]
Fine, you can come.
But I don't think you
and I have much more to say
to each other.
Sure we do.
And, even if we don't,
we can just go over
what we already
talked about again.
You're stubborn, you know that?
But hey.
I guess you never
were one to change.
No, I'm not!
[GROUP chuckles]
[YUE]
Hajime. Are they coming?
Yeah.
Seems like my former teacher
wants to look out for me.
She never compromises when
it comes to her students, so.
And leaving her behind would
make for way more trouble
when we got back.
I'm so excited to travel
with all these new people!
Uh...
Your motorcycle only seats
three people, right?
What about the rest of us?
[HAJIME] If you can't find
a seat, hop in the trunk.
Uh... Okay, everyone!
Here we go!
[TIO]
ARIFURETA:
From Commonplace
to World's Strongest.