Wow.
This is some entranceway.
Check out those pillars.
Think we made it?
[YUE]
To the Maverick's lair?
Hope so, because that
means we're one step closer.
We'll beat whatever's down here
and then we'll get the hell out.
Okay.
[HAJIME]
Crap!
Hey, look.
See how huge that circle is?
This's gotta be the big boss.
[YUE]
Don't worry.
We're strong, we won't lose.
Hell no.
We're taking this bastard down.
[HAJIME chuckles]
[HAJIME grunts]
Glacial Sleet!
[HAJIME growls]
[BEASTS growl]
[HAJIME chuckles]
[YUE] It looks like the
white one heals it.
[HAJIME]
All right, in that case...
...that one's the first to die!
Yue!
[YUE]
Crimson... Javelin!
[YUE, HAJIME gasp]
Okay, so the yellow
one's on defense.
One heals, one attacks,
one defends.
You're a well‐rounded
beastie, aren'tcha?
Take this!
[grunts]
[YUE]
Imperial Cannon!
[yelps]
[gasps]
[YUE]
What?
Is that me?
[YUE]
Hajime?
[YUE whimpers]
No!
Yue! Dammit!
[BEAST growls]
[HAJIME]
Get the hell away from her!
[HAJIME grunts]
[HAJIME growls]
[HAJIME]
Hey, wake up!
You've gotta snap out of it.
[YUE]
Hajime?
Yeah. Who else would it be?
You okay?
I was so frightened.
I thought I'd been
abandoned again.
Left alone in the darkness.
Listen up, we'll kill that
thing and get out of here,
make it to the surface,
and find a way home.
You and me.
Yeah!
That's settled.
Now how do we take it out?
[HAJIME]
I'm gonna try Schlagen.
I can only fire one shot
at a time, so I'll need cover.
[YUE]
I'm on it!
Just do what you need
to do‐‐I've got this!
[BEASTS screech, growl]
[YUE gasps]
[YUE]
Huh?
[YUE chuckles]
That won't work on me again!
[HAJIME growls]
[HAJIME] Using a debuff to scare
the crap out of its enemies.
That's pretty intense.
But you'll need more
than that against me!
[HAJIME grunts]
I'll take all of 'em
out in one go!
[HAJIME chuckles]
Heavenly Blaze!
[YUE gasps]
Look out!
[HAJIME gasps]
[YUE gasps]
[HAJIME grunting]
[YUE]
What happened?
[YUE gasps]
[YUE]
Are you okay?
No!
[YUE yelps]
[YUE]
Hajime!
You're bleeding!
[BEAST growls]
[YUE gasps]
Hang in there. I've got you.
[YUE]
Come on! Drink this for me!
[HAJIME coughs]
Hajime!
Please, you have to heal!
[BEAST growls]
It looks like it's
my turn to save you.
[BEAST growls]
[YUE yelps, gasps]
I can't stop.
I have to keep going.
[YUE grunts]
Please don't miss!
[YUE screaming]
[YUE]
I can't stop.
I have to save him.
[YUE gasps]
Hajime.
[YUE crying]
[HAJIME]
Yue. She's crying.
[BEAST growling]
[YUE]
I failed you.
I'm sorry.
Hey, stop crying. 'Kay?
You did great.
[YUE]
Hajime!
[HAJIME]
So slow.
Hurry! You need to run!
It's fine. Don't worry.
[HAJIME] Why do his attacks seem
so damn slow all of a sudden?
[YUE]
They're not slower.
You got faster somehow.
[HAJIME]
Yue, suck my blood.
We're gonna need
your magic soon.
So go on.
We've got a fight to win.
[HAJIME]
What the hell am I doing?
How long am I gonna
keep lying here?
[HAJIME]
If I don't get up,
I'm gonna lose her.
[YUE screaming]
[HAJIME]
Is that what I want?
To lose her to that monster?
My beloved... partner.
[YUE crying]
[HAJIME grunts]
I'll kill you!
[HAJIME] In that moment, I felt
something inside me awaken.
[HAJIME] Yue, when I give the
signal, cast Azure Blaze.
Focus on healing until then.
[YUE]
What about you?
[HAJIME]
Got a couple things to set up.
[HAJIME grunts]
You okay?
Hey, don't worry, I've got this.
[HAJIME grunts]
I've prepared a little
something special for you.
This is for hurting Yue!
[BEAST screeches]
[HAJIME]
Transmute!
Now it's time to close the trap!
[HAJIME]
Yue!
Azure Blaze!
[BEAST growling]
Hajime!
Sure hope we're done.
That's about all I got.
You did a great job.
I'm proud of you.
Yeah, back at'cha.
[AIKO]
You can't be serious!
You're going to
force those children
back into the fight already?
It's way too soon for that!
One of their friends
just died out there!
They should be taking time
to grieve and recover,
not heading back out
into battle again!
The loss of that noble young
man was unfortunate, indeed.
Then don't force
the other students to risk
meeting the same fate he did!
If you do, I won't assist
on the farms anymore.
Allow me to make a proposal.
We'll take only
those who volunteer.
Any who do not wish to fight
will not be required to.
I suppose that
will just have to do.
[ISHTAR]
Lady Aiko, as a Farmer,
your job is
incredibly important.
We humbly ask that you
continue using your abilities
to contribute to the
success of our agriculture.
[AIKO]
Excuse me.
Nagumo, class.
I should have stood up
for you much sooner.
But I'll do better from now on.
I promise.
[HAJIME screaming]
[SHIZUKU]
Kaori.
I'm okay. Don't mind me.
[SHIZUKU]
Take it easy, all right?
You're always
looking out for me.
[KOUKI] Kaori, I love how
kindhearted you are.
But we can't allow the
death of our classmate
to hold us back forever.
[SHIZUKU]
Hey, give her a break.
She needs to hear this, Shizuku.
Listen, we have to
keep moving forward.
I'm sure Nagumo would
want us to do our‐‐
I'm here for you,
so just let me know
if there's anything
I can do to help, okay?
Absolutely!
Whatever happens,
I've got your back 100%.
Thanks, Eri, Suzu.
That's so sweet of you.
[MELD]
All right, break's over!
Time to move out.
[KOUKI]
ARIFURETA:
From Commonplace to
World's Strongest.