[SHEA] Aww. How much longer
am I gonna have to wait?
Seriously, would they
just show up already?
[whines]
[growling]
[yelps]
[SHEA whimpering]
[screaming]
If they don't get here soon,
it's gonna be too late!
Come on!
Hurry and save me before
this thing catches me
and I end up as monster food.
Here they come!
[SHEA yells]
[SHEA grunts]
You're here!
You're finally here!
‐‐[YUE laughs]
‐‐[HAJIME] Yes!
[HAJIME]
We made it to the surface!
[YUE]
Mm‐hmm!
[SHEA] I've been waiting for
such a long time!
But here you are! Finally!
[HAJIME]
The hell is that?
[YUE]
A bunny girl?
And what'd she say? "Finally"?
Like she's been expecting
us or something?
Yeah. She's trouble. Let's go.
[SHEA]
Wait! Don't go!
I need your help!
[grunts]
Why would we help
a worthless rabbit?
[SHEA]
I'm begging you!
Please save my family!
[HAJIME]
Your family?
[SHEA whimpers]
Get off him.
No! I can't do that.
If I let go, you'll walk
away and leave me,
won't you?
Well, yeah, pretty much.
I don't see how I'm obligated
to help some bunny
I've never even met before.
[SHEA whines]
Shot down.
Could you really
abandon me like that?
A beautiful young
damsel in distress?
[HAJIME] Someone
thinks highly of herself.
[YUE]
Embarrassing.
[roars]
[SHEA yelps]
That thing.
Did it just roar at me?
[YUE]
Mm‐hmm.
No, wait! Stop!
You'll only get killed.
Let's run away while
we have the chance!
You took out a Diheadoar?
Wow! Amazing!
[HAJIME] C'mon, let's get
the hell out of here.
Without the extra baggage!
[SHEA yelps]
Please listen!
I am Shea, eldest daughter
of the Haulia beast tribe,
and we need your help.
If you save my family,
I'll do anything you ask of me!
Anything at all! Please help us!
[SHEA whines]
What's your major malfunction?
Just give up.
[SHEA]
I can't.
The future of my whole
race might be at stake.
[HAJIME]
All right, fine.
[SHEA yelps]
That really hurts! Ugh!
Well? Out with it.
What's your sob story?
[SHEA] Thank you so much
for giving me a chance.
Hey! Keep your
snotty‐ass nose off my coat!
That's freaking gross!
You jerk! I can't believe
you hit me again!
I'm a lady.
A beautiful young lady!
[HAJIME] How can you say this
crap with a straight face?
Especially in front of Yue,
who's a hundred times hotter
than you.
[YUE chuckles]
Yeah, well.
She may be pretty, but there's
gotta be at least one area
where I have her beat.
[gasps]
Oh, yeah, there totally is!
Look at her chest!
It's as flat as a boy's!
But mine's not.
What's wrong?
Are you hiding your face?
Aw, don't worry, I won't
tease you for blushing.
Huh?
Okay, you're mad.
Would it help if I said sorry?
Any last words before you die?
[SHEA]
No! Please don't kill me!
[HAJIME] So your tribe's
got monster trouble.
But why were you exiled
in the first place?
[SHEA] Beastmen aren't supposed
to be able to manipulate mana,
but for some reason, I can.
And on top of that, I can use
a special kind of magic
that only monsters use.
Why's it so special?
[SHEA]
Well, It's called Future Sight.
I see possible futures.
Like, if you make
a certain choice,
then this is what will happen.
You know?
Actually, that's how
I knew I'd meet you.
[gasps]
Please! Will you help us?
If you don't, then the
Haulia race is doomed!
[HAJIME]
Not happening.
[SHEA]
Please! Hear me out!
I saw this!
I saw into the future!
You help us!
You save me and my
people from the monsters!
Oh, do I?
And what do I get
for this noble act?
Huh?
[HAJIME]
Well? Nothing, right?
[SHEA] Wait.
You're headed for the Great Tree
in the Haltsina Sea
of Trees, aren't you?
Well, you should know
it's surrounded by fog.
Really thick fog, too.
People get
hopelessly lost in it.
So?
[SHEA]
So, if you had someone with you,
someone who was
a native of the Sea of Trees...
Let's take her.
[HAJIME]
Really?
Having a guide could be helpful.
[SHEA] You're the best!
Thank you so much!
It's okay.
I'm sure you'll warm up
to me eventually.
[RABBIT GIRL 6A]
Look! Look!
I found some fruit.
Don't they look yummy?
Wait! Get back here!
[CAM]
No!
[RABBIT GIRL 6A screams]
[SHEA]
Father, I'm home!
I'm back, and I
brought help with me!
[laughing]
[CAM]
Shea!
[RABBITMEN]
Huh?
[SHEA]
Everyone!
We're saved!
Owie.
[HAJIME] If you and your big
mouth are gonna get in the way,
I guess I'll have
to put you to work.
What do you mean, "work"?
[HAJIME]
Don't worry.
It's an easy job, and one
that you'll be perfect for.
Acting as bait for
those monsters.
Go get 'em,
you worthless rabbit!
[SHEA]
No!
[screaming]
[SHEA yelps]
[RABBITMEN gasp]
So scary!
I can't take it!
I'm fragile, you know,
and you're being awfully
rough with me... ah!
[grunts]
Treat me like the delicate
young lady I am, please?
Because I can use the same
powers monsters can,
my fate was to be detested,
and eventually killed,
by the other beastmen.
My father and the
rest of the Haulia tribe
refused to let that happen.
In order to protect me, they
left our home of Verbergen
and came to live out here.
But rabbitmen aren't fighters.
We have no way
to protect ourselves
from the dangers of this world.
[RABBITMEN snoring]
[SHEA] I never thought it
possible that my people
would know this kind of peace.
Thank you both so much.
Save your thanks.
It's all just part of the deal.
We protect your people,
and in exchange,
you guide us to the tree.
[SHEA] I've never met
anyone like you before.
Someone who could
use monstrous powers
like I can.
It may sound strange,
but I feel a sort of kinship
with you.
Can I ask what the goal
of your journey is?
[HAJIME]
It's simple enough.
I'm taking Yue and going home.
That's my goal.
[SHEA]
I've been thinking,
and I made a decision.
I'm going to join you
on your journey.
[HAJIME]
No thanks.
[YUE]
Yeah, you'll just hold us back.
[SHEA]
Shot down again!
Huh?
We want to get stronger.
I'm tired of feeling weak.
Hajime, sir.
Please, we beseech you.
Do you, now?
I've got you!
[SHEA screaming]
[RABBITMEN crying]
[RABBITMEN chattering]
[HAJIME growls]
[HAJIME]
Hey.
[CAM]
Yes?
[HAJIME] We're in a forest
surrounded by plants.
Don't tell me you
idiots are all sappy
because of that flower.
[CAM]
Ooh! We can't help it.
It has pretty petals and
these cute little bugs
crawling on it.
Nature really is amazing,
don't you think?
[HAJIME growls]
[RABBIT BOY 6A]
He killed the flower!
[CAM]
Hajime, sir!
[HAJIME]
How have you survived this long?
Listen up, you
crap‐for‐brains rabbits!
If you don't want me to murder
each and every one of you,
then slay a monster for me!
It's kill or be killed!
[SHEA yells]
[YUE]
Crimson Javelin.
[SHEA]
It's not over yet!
[SHEA yells]
[YUE]
Flame fortress.
[SHEA]
I've got you now!
[YUE]
Wind wall!
Crystal Coffin!
Hey. Wait. Don't‐‐
‐‐[SHEA] So... cold...
‐‐[YUE] Looks like I win.
Aw, man. Not again.
[gasps] Hold on!
Look at your cheek!
There's a mark there!
I totally hit you
with an attack!
This is the best day ever!
You're seeing things.
I promise, there was a scratch!
Don't pretend like I didn't
hit you, you cheater!
[sneezes]
[SHEA whimpers]
That was so cold. Jeez!
For a second, I was positive
I was gonna freeze to death!
You done dueling yet?
I'm sure Yue won.
Nope!
I managed to scratch her face,
so this was my glorious victory!
I wish you could've seen it!
You know...
It's not often you meet someone
with both beauty and brawn.
Right.
So, Yue. How'd she do?
[YUE] She's worked hard
to strengthen her body,
giving her a monstrous
level of power.
Well, damn. Good for you.
You see?
Please let me come
on your journey.
I'll be a big help.
Why exactly do you
wanna join us?
Oh. Well, the thing is,
I just kinda...
Just what? Out with it.
[SHEA] I just wanna
be with you, Hajime!
Because I wuv you!
[HAJIME]
Huh?
[CAM]
'Ey boss.
We hunted down every last
monster we could find.
Whoa. Father?
Your voice is weird.
You seem so different.
That many?
I only said you needed
to bring me one monster.
[CAM] A whole pack of
'em attacked our party,
they had the nerve
to try to kill us,
so we cut the fiends to shreds.
Like you said.
Kill or be killed.
They were annoying,
but their dying screams
filled me with so
much raw pleasure.
Um, Hajime... Question.
What did you teach my people?
How to survive.
That's the Great Tree?
[CAM] It's been dead
since before Verbergen
was established.
But it never rotted away.
It's stood here for ages,
lifeless but unchanging.
[HAJIME] Up there.
It looks like Oscar's ring.
[YUE]
Yes. It's the same design.
That settles it.
We found the entrance
to another labyrinth.
[HAJIME]
What's this?
[YUE] This door will open
once more only to those
who possess the four symbols,
the power of regeneration,
and a beacon
formed out of ironclad bonds.
[SHEA]
What's that mumbo jumbo mean?
We need four symbols?
Then maybe those
are the labyrinth relics?
Ah. And that part about
the beacon formed of bonds
might be the fact
that you joined up
with some super‐brave beastmen.
The magic of teamwork!
But the power of regeneration.
I don't think that's
gonna get us through.
[YUE] Hmm. Perhaps if we
clear the other labyrinths,
we'll learn more ancient magic.
And in doing so, we'll gain
the regeneration ability
needed to get in.
[SHEA]
I get it now.
[HAJIME]
What a pain.
Guess we've gotta head to
those other Maverick dungeons
before we do this one.
Hear that?
I can't get inside.
That means I've got to
track down other labyrinths.
Our deal is officially over.
This is where we part ways.
Good luck, I guess.
With what you learned,
you should be able to survive
out here by yourselves now.
[CAM]
Boss! Please.
Let us travel alongside you.
We beg you.
[HAJIME]
No.
[CAM]
We'll follow behind you, then.
[HAJIME]
Nah, just keep training.
That's the best thing
you can do to help.
That way, when I come back,
maybe you'll be useful.
You hear that, everyone?
We're gonna keep on training
till we're strong enough
to help out the boss.
[RABBITMEN cheer]
[SHEA]
Mother.
Am I a monster
or am I a beastman?
[SHEA'S MOM] A white shadow
lurks in the Sea of Trees,
but is never fully revealed,
always vanishing
the second before you see it.
It must be a new
type of monster.
Something terrifying.
One that's lived here
since the dawn of time.
[SHEA whimpers]
I bet you went out again
and heard people talking.
You hear everything with
these floppy ears of yours.
[SHEA whimpers]
[SHEA'S MOM]
Do you want to be a monster?
Of course not.
That would be terrible!
And why's that?
[SHEA]
Um... What do you mean?
I understand it
doesn't always feel like
a good thing to be different.
It can be lonely
or frightening or sad.
But here's a secret.
There are some things you can do
only because you're different.
Ways that you can
help other people.
Like someone special to you.
Wow, really, Mom?
Why don't we talk
about the future?
One day, you'll meet
some wonderful people
outside the Sea of Trees.
In fact, I think they'll
be a lot like you.
What do you mean by that?
I promise there's no way
you're the only person
who's different in this world.
It's a pretty big place.
From outside the Sea of Trees.
They're out there.
I know it.
[SHEA]
You were right, Mother.
Thank you.
[SHEA gasps]
Hey, Yue!
You promised me something
if I landed an attack!
I know you remember.
I get to come with you!
Tra‐vel bud‐dies!
Fine. Just try to
keep quiet, okay?
[SHEA laughs]
[YUE]
Hajime.
Let's take this
worthless rabbit with us.
So those were the
stakes of your duel, huh?
Sadly.
So is it okay, then?
You can come with us.
But that doesn't mean we're
gonna get along with you.
The future isn't absolute,
don't you know that?
Anything can happen!
And I believe that if
I try hard enough,
I can change the future
all by my lonesome.
It can be hard, you know.
This power of mine.
Sometimes I try to stop
bad things from happening,
but they still do.
And I always wonder
if maybe it's because
I didn't do my best.
But from now on, I don't
want to have any regrets.
It's gonna be dangerous.
Well, then,
I'm glad I'm a monster!
If it gets scary,
I can take care of myself.
Yeah, about that...
It'll be hard for you
to live in my world.
I don't care! Really!
[SHEA]
Is that all you've got?
Great. Then that means I win!
Wait, what?
I mean, I won you over.
We're getting closer.
Whatever.
Weirdo.
[RABBITMEN chuckle]
[YUE]
Hmph.
[RYUTARO]
Arifureta:
From Commonplace
to World's Strongest.