[giggles]
An ambush?
I'll give you credit
for making it this far
but you've reached
the end of the line.
We've come here
to rescue our friend,
and we'll be taking
our super-secret
ninja art scroll back, too.
Dare to get in our way,
and we'll show you no mercy!
If you think you
can come into our school
and take that haughty tone with
me, you're gravely mistaken.
You spoiled rich girls
are always so demanding.
What, are you going
to slap me across the face
with a wad of bills next?
[KATSURAGI] It's on!
♪
[HARUKA] Judging from
the noise above,
I think it's safe to say
your friends have arrived.
They're here?
So, is everything going
according to your plan, Sensei?
[HARUKA] You may think that
you have the upper hand,
but it's only a matter of time
before we prove you wrong.
Please don't fight!
You shouldn't be
challenging anyone,
not when your lives
are on the line!
Just relax. There's
no reason to worry
because we've no
chance of losing.
I wouldn't be so sure.
Well, well, Sensei.
I wondered when
you'd finally speak up.
You shouldn't
underestimate Hanzo,
or their shinobi teacher,
Kiriya, for that matter.
[SUZUNE] Every time
a student loses a battle,
they examine the reason why.
[SUZUNE] They remedy
their shortcomings,
and they work to improve
any advantages they may have.
Each loss makes them stronger.
[grunts]
[HARUKA] Are you saying
that you pushed us to fight the
Hanzo Academy girls in order to
help them develop their skills?
You're free to
assume whatever you like
but it was a simple
statement, dear.
All I wanted was for you
girls to face opponents who
would measure up to you.
Sensei, I can't help but
wonder whose side you're on.
I suppose it
doesn't really matter.
After all, you're the one who
rescued me from hell on earth
so I'm forever in your debt.
Please, Haruka.
What did I just tell you?
There's no need to worry;
and the next time we meet
I'm going to add you
to my collection permanently.
[Yomi yells]
I want you girls
to go on without me!
[IKARUGA] I'm going to stay
here and deal with her myself!
What? No, way!
We can't just leave
you with that psycho!
Let me guess,
you've got some sort of
personal vendetta against me?
I don't. That's
why I have to do this.
Shinobi kekkai!
[gasp]
Ikaruga!
No, come back!
[YAGYU] Let's get a move on.
[KATSURAGI] I hope
she'll be alright!
She's not gonna lose this fight.
I get it.
What kinda team would we be
if we didn't have faith
in each other, right?
You ready to go out there
and kick some butt?
You bet!
♪
[KATSURAGI] It's like
a freakin' maze in here!
I thought our school
was hard to navigate
but it's tiny compared
to this place!
I dunno where we're goin' but
we gotta keep movin' forward!
[HIBARI] Um. Excuse me?
Is it true that you used to be
a student at Hanzo Academy?
[HIBARI] Why'd you
become an evil ninja?
So, you've been to
Shinobi Island before.
You went there
for training, right?
And you're the one who wrote
"Hang in there.
Super-ninja or bust!"
I mean, I could be
wrong but I've got this
really weird feeling
that it was you.
How'd you know?
It was just a hunch, 'cause
an image of that writing
popped into my head
when we first met.
So I figured it was you.
To think he was
able to teach one of his
shinobi students how to tap
into the Second Sight technique.
Impressive, Kiriya-sensei.
[HIBARI] I have no idea
what you're talking about.
He never taught me
anything like that!
[SUZUNE] Ninjutsu is
a skill of the mind.
As intellect grows,
technique develops.
Strengthening those techniques,
in turn, strengthens the mind.
[Hibari gasp]
[shaky breath]
[PATROL NINJA 1] Hurry!
We can't let Suzune escape!
[ALL] Ugh!
But what will
happen if you lose?
[SUZUNE] You must be
willing to risk your life
for what is most
important to you.
That's what it means
to be a shinobi.
What's most important?
[YOMI] Dragging me into a
kekkai for a one-on-one fight.
Goodness, you seem awfully
sure of yourself, rich girl.
[Yomi power yell]
[YOMI] Just so
you know, I find you
utterly disagreeable
in every way!
I've always felt
that way about you!
Always?
You lived in the
mansion up on the hill.
[YOMI] Those of us who were poor
were forced to grow up in the
shadows of your palatial home,
forever looking down on us.
[gasp]
[FEMALE INTERVIEWER] I'd
like to talk a little more
about the charitable
side of business.
I know a great deal of
money has been donated
via NPO contributions...
[YOUNG YOMI] That's the
girl... who lives up there.
[IKARUGA'S FATHER] Well,
big business is obligated
to help the less fortunate,
especially the children,
of this world.
"Big business"
never did anything
to help me and my family!
My parents had to give me the
little food they could afford,
while they starved to death!
Your family is the very
reason mine fell apart!
[YOMI] You may not have killed
my parents with your own hands,
but your father's false promises
are what led to their demise!
Secret ninja art! Niflheim!
[gasp]
She wasn't
fazed by my attack!
[IKARUGA] You had a family who
loved you so much they gave
their very lives so
that you might survive.
[gasp]
I don't think you realize
just how lucky you are.
If my family
cared half as much,
I wouldn't have
suffered like I did.
[YOMI] I'm "lucky"?
You have no idea what
I've been through!
[IKARUGA] Same goes for me.
Now let's go!
There's only one way
for us to settle this!
[KATSURAGI] Ahhh!
[KATSURAGI]
We gotta get back up!
It's no use!
We're trapped.
Katsu! Yagyu!
[YAGYU] No, don't
come down here!
[KATSURAGI] I hate
to break it to ya,
but it looks like everything's
ridin' on you now, Asuka.
On me?
Don't worry 'bout us.
Go find those Hebijo hoes
and show 'em that Hanzo
shinobi mean business!
But Katsu!
Go!
No, I can't!
What are you
waiting for? Hurry!
Alright.
[EVIL NINJAS] Ahhh!
[Katsuragi yell]
[evil ninjas scream]
[MIRAI] Aw shucks.
It appears that one
of them has escaped.
[HIKAGE] Unfortunately, the
trap didn't trigger in time
to catch the shinobi Asuka.
She's a lot faster
than I thought she'd be.
Geez.
You say that as if
you're impressed with her.
[KATSURAGI] Ha! I knew
you'd be lurkin' around here!
[MIRAI] Well, this
works out perfectly.
I was hoping to take
my revenge on you!
I guess that means
I get to go another round
against you, blondie.
Good, I've been
looking forward to it!
You disgust me!
[MIRAI] I've hated you from
the moment I laid eyes on you!
Where is Hibari being hidden?
Don't you dare
ignore me, pigtails!
Ready, Katsu?
Let's do it.
[power yell]
Shinobi kekkai!
Hate that I had to
copy Ikaruga, but oh well.
[HIKAGE] Is this necessary?
I mean, you're only gonna lose.
Well, you won't be
able to ignore me anymore
now that we're in a kekkai.
I came here to protect
my friend Hibari.
Not listen to you.
[HIKAGE] Why is it that you
want to fight me so badly?
Because ever since
you kicked my butt,
all I could think about
was returnin' the favor!
Now that I've got the chance,
I'm not gonna blow it!
Let me to give you a
word of advice, blondie.
Advice?
[HIKAGE] You should never
talk while fighting,
'cause you'll bite your tongue.
Fine, then I'll
get right to it!
[HIKAGE] That look in her eyes.
[MAN] Fear. Pity. Anger.
In our line of work,
emotion can prove fatal,
so you must learn
to suppress it.
Go after your target with a
cool head and you'll increase
your chances of survival.
[HIKAGE] When I look in
her eyes, it's like she's
reaching within me to bring
those suppressed emotions
to the surface.
[KATSURAGI] Ha!
[HIKAGE] Ugh.
Why're you just
standin' there? Bring it!
It feels... like a
wave of sadness hit me.
How bizarre.
It's hard to believe
I ever had these feelings.
What're you babblin'
to yourself about?
Get over here and fight!
[HIKAGE] You don't
have to tell me twice.
Ready to die?
Secret ninja art! Thrust!
Let's see what you've got!
[Katsuragi breathing heavy]
I'm not gonna lose to you.
Oh really?
Well, one of us has to lose
and it ain't gonna be me!
[grunts]
You're not the only person here
who's trying to protect
something they cherish!
I am, too, y'know.
[Young Mirai crying]
Here, watch me do it.
[gasp]
[HOMURA] Okay,
now you give it a try.
[MIRAI] I also have something...
...that's worth fighting for!
I know that.
What? How? You don't
know anything about me!
[Yagyu power yell]
[MIRAI] Ahhh!
You're right, I may not know
what it is you hold dear,
but I do know this...
All of us have something,
that we would give
our lives to protect.
[MIRAI] My friends,
'cause they don't ignore me.
Understandable,
there's nothing worse
than being ignored.
I feel the same way!
I really hate myself
for agreeing with you!
Secret ninja art!
Valkyrie, fire!
[YAGYU] Ahhh!
[gunfire]
[both power yell]
You're not too bad.
Well, neither are you.
Okay, one more
floor and I'm golden!
It's just you?
Whaddya mean?
[HOMURA] I never
would've expected you to be
the last good
girl left standing.
[ASUKA] What have
you done with Hibari?
[HOMURA] Unfortunately,
she got caught eavesdropping,
so we've got her
locked up in a cell.
What the heck
was she thinking?
I bet that she was trying
to get the scroll back!
[HOMURA] If you
wanna go any farther,
you're gonna
have to get past me.
Good luck, Asuka!
Shinobi kekkai!
Homura! I'm
gonna take you down!
Ha! Yeah right, you wish.
Uh-oh, what a shame!
I turned my back
and I lost a prisoner.
[HARUKA] How careless of me.
I'm begging you, Haruka.
Please let me outta here!
And why should I do that?
[HIBARI] I need to
tell my friends about
the yoke technique!
I've gotta warn them 'cause you
guys'll die if they beat you!
What's it matter?
Huh?
[HARUKA] The only way you and
your friends will be able
to complete your mission is if
you can defeat us in battle.
I don't wanna complete
the mission if it means
you guys're gonna die!
[HARUKA] Well, if our
time's up, then so be it.
Like it or not,
we've been ordered
to go out there
and risk it all.
We've no choice but to fight.
It's our penance for being
saved from our living hell.
[HIBARI] You never told me
how you ended up here.
Why did you
become an evil ninja?
[HARUKA] My father is
the general director
of a large hospital.
[HIBARI] He is?
[HARUKA] His public
reputation was impeccable,
but in reality, he was
a despicably evil man.
He silenced malpractice
cases with cash he made
by cheating on his taxes.
[HARUKA] He rarely spent
any time at home with me
and my mother, but not
because he was working.
I'm sure you can guess why.
Instead of taking her
frustrations out on him,
my mother doted on me.
No, I take that back.
It wasn't so much
that she doted on me,
as I was her dress-up doll.
A toy for her to play with.
[HARUKA'S MOTHER] How adorable!
You look precious!
Then when I
started middle school,
I found it harder to deal
with my mother's smothering.
But instead of speaking up,
I buried my feelings.
[HARUKA] You can only hide
your emotions for so long
before your sanity
starts breaking down.
[YOUNG HARUKA] If I
just burn everything,
then that'll be the end of it.
Finally, I can be free
once and for all.
[gasp]
[SUZUNE] Didn't anyone ever
teach you not to play with fire?
I had no idea that
Suzune-sensei had been
scouting me for Hebijo Academy.
[HARUKA] She certainly
has a keen eye.
[HARUKA] While the mere thought
of death might terrify you,
we aren't afraid because we've
been pulled from the brink
of death once already.
I'm free?
[HARUKA] Well, not to roam
the castle but you're free
to fight me if you wish.
Let's see if you've got what it
takes to defeat me in battle.
[HARUKA] What's
the matter? C'mon!
Don't you wanna
take a shot at me?
[HIBARI] Shinobi
transformation!
[HIBARI] I'm gonna do this
all by myself, Yagyu!
You just watch!
You don't have to
worry about me anymore.
[HIBARI] Shinobi kekkai!
[HARUKA] My,
isn't this charming?
[HIBARI] I've got a question
about the yoke technique,
do you know if you have some
time before it takes effect
or does it happen right away?
Hmmm. I'm afraid I don't have
an answer for you, my dear.
[HIBARI] Huh?
It activates
when the person who cast
the technique
acknowledges our loss.
You see, there's a
surprisingly fine line
between winning and losing.
So, all we have to do
is keep the headmaster
from activating it!
Now don't you
think you might be
getting ahead
of yourself, cutie?
[HARUKA] You don't
honestly believe that you
and your friends can
defeat us, do you?
[HARUKA] Why don't you
just give up, Hibari?
I may be down but
this fight isn't over.
[HIBARI] I'm not the
weakling, that you think I am.
I'm gonna win.
You just watch me!
Secret ninja art.
Come to me.
[rumbling]
[bunny yell]
[HARUKA] I won't fall
for the same trick twice!
My, that was careless of me.
Hey guys.
I hope you can hear me!
Hibari!
[HIBARI] Don't
fight the evil ninja!
What do you mean? Why not?
If they lose in battle,
the headmaster'll activate
the yoke technique
and they'll die!
[KATSURAGI] Seriously?
If they lose, they die?
I promise I'll explain
it all to you later!
But for now, just try
not to fight them!
Oh no!
I had no idea
Hibari was capable
of such powerful telepathy.
[ASUKA] Is that true?
If you lose this fight,
you'll lose your life?
Yep, that's
what happens when
the yoke
technique's invoked.
How can you act like
it's no big deal that
you're risking your life?
[HOMURA] 'Cause it's not
a big deal. If I fail, I die.
Whatever. Personally,
I think that's the way
it oughta be for all shinobi.
Homura. How
could you say that?
You've got it all wrong!
But why did you
let him do this to you?
Now, now, there's
no need to worry.
Nothing will happen to us unless
we lose and that's not likely.
[KATSURAGI] That's messed up.
That's how it goes.
[KATSURAGI] How can
you be so nonchalant?
Don't you care if you die?
Drama queen.
She just had to go and
tell everybody, didn't she?
Hibari!
I'm so glad to hear
that she's safe!
[MIRAI] Hey! I'm
still here ya' know!
I told you how much
I hate being ignored!
Ugh. What?
I'm not going to fight you.
Not when your survival
depends on the outcome.
We've gotta find the
headmaster on the top level!
He's the only one that
can lift the yoke technique.
[HIBARI] And I'll grab the
scroll while I'm up there!
Not if I stop you!
Secret ninja art Death Kiss!
[HIBARI] Ahhh!
[HARUKA] Finally.
It's time for you to become
my little puppet, cutie.
[ALL] Secret ninja art!
[IKARUGA] Phoenix
Flame Flash, One!
Ahhh!
[screaming]
[KATSURAGI] Tornado Spindel!
[KATSURAGI] Ha!
[dinging]
[MIRAI] Ahhh!
We've gotta find this
headmaster douche bag!
Hey! Tell me how we
can get to the top level!
Why should I?
What good is goin'
up there gonna do?
As shinobi we have to
be ready to take the lives
of others to complete
our mission.
It sucks, but at least we have
control over our own lives!
[KATSURAGI] Why
would you give that up?
You're outta luck. The
only path is sealed off.
Someone's helpin' them.
Let's head to the top, Yagyu!
You go on without me.
[KATSURAGI] What?
I think Hibari's voice
was coming from below us.
So I'm gonna look for her.
Okay. Then go
do what you gotta do!
But you weren't this strong
the last time we fought.
[IKARUGA] Ninjutsu is a skill
of the mind and right now
mine is exceedingly frustrated.
We should be joining
forces to take down the jerk
who's controlling you, and not
fighting against each other.
You think?
I don't know
how to explain it,
but this added power is
a reflection of my pride
as a good ninja.
[YOMI] Well, good for you.
It must be nice to be
so incredibly fortunate.
There's something
you should know about
what you saw on TV that day.
You see, the only reason my
father did that interview
was to announce
he was adopting a child.
Hold on, you mean,
you were adopted?
He claimed to be a
philanthropist who opened
his heart to a girl who had
lost all her relatives,
but the truth is he was forced
to adopt me to carry on
the shinobi family line because
his own son was a failure.
[Yomi gasp]
All I have to my name is my
mission to live as a shinobi.
And there's not
a drop's worth of
familial affection to be found.
Uh.
[YOMI] Why? Why did you
choose to tell me all of this?
[crying] It's not fair.
How am I supposed
to hate you now?!
[ASUKA] I know that whenever
we fall on hard times,
we can move past it, as
long as we work together
and look out for one another.
Next time, the final
episode of Senran Kagura
Ninja Flash,
"Super-Secret Ninja Art".
Come and get it like
your life depends on it!