I don't mean to make a fuss
but it doesn't seem very fair.
I mean, I have no problem
with the rising prices
of high-grade vegetables
since they're usually
only purchased by the wealthy.
Okay.
[YOMI] But raising the cost of
sprouts, a staple in the diet
of the underprivileged,
seems incredibly unfair.
Wouldn't you agree?
I dunno. It's kinda hard
to answer that impartially
when you've got a weapon
pointed right at me.
[YOMI] I would've asked you.
But you've never
had to eat sprouts.
Wait! What'd she mean by that?
It doesn't matter, we were told
not to interact
with the public.
But I've got a
feeling that she's a--
What a shame.
I was hoping we could
take care of this in
a more civilized manner.
[sigh]
Shinobi kekkai!
[BOTH] Uh.
[ASUKA] She is a
ninja! I knew it!
[IKARUGA] What
do you want with us?
You're the one I'm after.
Aren't you the daughter of
one of Japan's
wealthiest businessmen?
[IKARUGA] What
does it matter to you?
You were raised
in a loving home with
parents who lavished
you with affection
and bought you everything
your heart desired.
It must have been nice.
You're a lucky girl.
You lead a privileged
life and want for nothing.
[Yomi chuckling]
I think she wants to fight!
Just stand back and
let me handle this, Asuka.
Why?
Because she's made
it perfectly clear
that I'm the one she's after.
[grunt]
[IKARUGA]
Shinobi Transformation!
[IKARUGA] I was hoping
it wouldn't come to this,
but you've left me no choice!
Now, prepare yourself to fight!
♪
Lavender in Full Bloom!
[Ikaruga struggling]
[gasp]
Ha!
Ikaruga, no!
She's stronger than I thought.
Underestimate me, did you?
It's a shame all that money
couldn't buy you any power.
Rose Melody!
[gasp]
[grunt]
[power yell]
Secret Ninja Art... Niflheim!
[IKARUGA] Ahhh!
[NARRATOR] When a transformed
shinobi takes damage in battle,
their uniform
dissolves, leaving them
in little more than a bikini.
It's a win-win situation
for everyone involved.
If our heroines win, awesome!
If they lose, still awesome!
Ikaruga, are you okay?
No. How did this happen?
She defeated me.
[YOMI] Is that all you've got?
I expected more
from you "good ninjas".
What did you call us?
There's only one reason
you'd refer to us by that name.
Because you're evil!
Now why in the hell are
you attacking us like this?
Do you think you can
take that tone with me
just because you're
wealthier than I am?
Well, thankfully, I don't have
to stand for such nonsense.
[YOMI] I've had enough of
you and your highborn ways.
I'll take my leave but I'll
be back to finish you off.
[ASUKA] You took a direct hit!
Are you sure you're all right?
I'll be fine,
just give me a second.
I couldn't do anything.
I just stood there.
[IKARUGA] I can't believe we
actually picked up everything
that we need for Master
Hanzo's welcoming party
and somehow we still managed
to stay well within our budget.
Yeah, I guess so.
All we have left to do is cook
and then it's party time!
I'm sorry, but I have to ask.
How did that girl know you
come from a wealthy family?
[ASUKA] It's not
like you flaunt it.
If another shinobi wants
information on us all
they have to do is look it up.
Good point and I'll
bet there's all kinds
of info on you
since you're part of
such a famous
and wealthy family.
C'mon, we need to hurry.
[ASUKA] Uh... Hey!
Wait up, Ikaruga!
[IKARUGA] I'm
terribly sorry, Sensei!
Hmm?
[IKARUGA] I disregarded
your order and interacted
with the public.
I must be punished!
[KIRIYA] That's not necessary.
You didn't have any
choice in the matter.
[IKARUGA] But sir, violating
an order is the most
shameful thing
a shinobi can do!
[KIRIYA] Stop being so formal.
It's not the end of the world.
Maybe not to you,
but I won't be able to
forgive myself until
I've been disciplined.
[IKARUGA] Go on, Sensei!
Punish me however you see fit!
Uh...
[HANZO] You should
do as she says.
[gasp]
[BOTH] Master Hanzo!
Here's the thing, the young
lady has a valid argument.
She obviously takes great
pride in being a shinobi.
Well yes, that's
true but-- I don't know--
If you don't feel
comfortable punishing Ikaruga,
I'd be more than
happy to do it for you.
Thank you for your
understanding, Master Hanzo!
Now I'm worried.
[Ikaruga breathing heavy]
[HANZO] Aw, yeah.
[HANZO] That's a good girl.
Go a little deeper.
[IKARUGA] Yes, sir!
[Ikaruga breathing heavy]
[HANZO] Oh... There
ya go! That's it, Ikaruga!
[IKARUGA] Oh,
Master Hanzo!
Wow! How does a man
your age still get so stiff?
[IKARUGA] Ah!
[Hanzo moaning]
[Ikaruga breathing heavy]
[HANZO] The older ya are,
the more stiff ya get.
Ah, right there!
Ooh, I'm next!
Ikaruga's gonna be a pro
when she's done with you!
[ASUKA] Geez. Are you
seriously gonna make her
massage your
entire body, Grandpa?
Well, she did say that she
wanted to be punished, so--
Ah! Yeah, right there!
[ASUKA] Hey Ikaruga,
lemme take over for you.
No, that's okay.
Aw come on? I used to
do it for him all the time.
I kinda miss it.
Besides, I know how to
work out his
knots in no time.
[IKARUGA] Oh, really? Well,
in that case, go right ahead.
[Asuka giggles]
[Hanzo moaning]
[ASUKA] Whenever I
give Grandpa a massage
it reminds me
of being back home.
[HANZO] You know, Asuka,
massage is supposed to
loosen muscles,
not bruise them!
You always told me that
beggars can't be choosers
so stop your
complaining, would ya?
[moan in pain]
[chuckles]
Who'd have thought the
legendary Master Hanzo
could be taken
down by a bad massage?
Yeah, no joke.
But it's nice to see
a sweet family
moment like this.
Wha--? There ain't
nothin' sweet about it!
[explosion]
[all coughing]
Sorry for holding up dinner.
So, what caused you to be late?
A phone call.
Ikaruga's family is
quite frantic at the moment.
Is everything all right?
You guys got attacked
by an evil ninja?
So what was she like?
Well, I dunno.
She was really
snobby and frilly.
That's not what I meant.
Like, was she super strong?
Oh yeah. There's no
way I could've fought her
on my own. She totally
would've kicked my butt.
I'm sorry I wasn't strong
enough to help you, Ikaruga.
It's okay. I'm
the one who ordered you
to stay clear of the fight.
[KATSURAGI] No way! So
it was just you against her?
Yeah! You knocked that
hoe-bag's teeth in, didn't ya?
No, I simply refused
to continue fighting her.
As shinobi, it is our duty to
avoid pointless altercations.
Geez. If it had
been me, I would've
manhandled that evil skank!
Watch, I'll show you!
[KATSURAGI]
C'mere you evil doer!
[ASUKA] What's with you?
[KATSURAGI] I'm gonna
squeeze the evil out!
[KATSURAGI] Gimme
those wicked wobblies!
[IKARUGA] I lied. I
didn't refuse to fight her.
I knew I wasn't
strong enough to win.
[KIRIYA] Ikaruga.
Yes, sir?
May I have a moment?
[IKARUGA] Sure.
Is somethin' wrong?
Don't worry.
Just finish your dinner.
[Hibari sigh]
[YAGYU] Hm.
[HANZO] How cute!
I can tell that you girls
are really good friends.
Yeah, we're the
bestest friends ever.
Aren't we, Yagyu?
I just do my best
to keep Hibari safe
because she's always
getting into trouble.
[HIBARI] That's not true!
Quit treating me like a baby!
She's just worried
because she cares about you.
Now tell me, are
you girls so close
that you take baths together?
Yes, sir!
[HIBARI] We even wash each
other's backs and everything!
Well, if you girls
ever need help
I'm an excellent back washer!
Didn't I tell you?
No perving out over
my friends, Grandpa!
I'm not "pervin' out".
I'm simply offering my
services to these young ladies.
[KATSURAGI] Master Hanzo
suffers from the same
disease I do, funbag-itis!
[ASUKA] Ahhh!
[Hanzo chuckling]
[IKARUGA] What do you mean
my brother's gone missing?
Your family called earlier.
They can't find him anywhere
and they were hoping
you might know
his whereabouts.
Why do they think I
would know where he is?
My brother and I
don't really talk,
and we've never
been all that close.
[KIRIYA] I see.
[IKARUGA] I'm sorry.
[KIRIYA] Oh, no. Don't
apologize, I just wanted
to ask in case you
happened to know something.
They are your
family, after all.
My family. Yes, of course.
[grunt]
Gonna stand out
here all night?
No. I felt like
someone was watching me.
What?
[HIBARI] Huh?
[ASUKA] Well, I
don't see anybody.
I'm sorry I guess that
it was just my imagination.
But you're usually spot-on.
We all have our off days.
So, we've got half an hour
and then it's
time to hit the sack.
[ASUKA] Yes ma'am!
[HIBARI] Gotcha!
[KATSURAGI] What kinda party
ends before the sun comes up?
[IKARUGA] The evil ninja
attack and the disappearance
of my brother must be
making me a little jumpy.
[IKARUGA'S FATHER] As
of today, she is a member
of our immediate family.
Say hello to
your brother, dear.
Hi. Nice to meet you.
So tell me somethin'.
How much money did
my old man pay for you?
[IKARUGA'S FATHER] Watch
your mouth, Murasame!
She's a distant relative.
[MURASAME] Yeah,
whatever you say.
[gasp]
[MURASAME] Like it matters.
It doesn't change the fact
that you've
forsaken me, Father.
[IKARUGA'S FATHER]
That's enough out of you!
[chuckles]
[IKARUGA] I think he hates me.
[IKARUGA'S FATHER]
Don't worry about him.
There are times when we
are forced to be resolute,
even with our
own flesh and blood.
That is the
law of the shinobi.
[Ikaruga shaky gasp]
[IKARUGA] What is this?
[IKARUGA'S FATHER]
Hien. A sword that's been
in our family for generations.
Now I'm handing it
down to you, my daughter.
[IKARUGA] To me?
Thank you, Father!
[NARRATOR] After realizing
their son, Murasame,
wasn't cut out to be a ninja,
Ikaruga's family adopted her
to carry on their
shinobi bloodline.
[IKARUGA] Brother.
Why did you run away?
[Ikaruga gasp]
Who's there?
[MURASAME] Well,
well, aren't you slick?
Brother, it's you!
Long time no see.
[IKARUGA] Brother.
What're you doing here?
Why do you
keep calling me that?
It's not like you're
my actual little sister.
[IKARUGA] What do you think
you're doing with Hien?
[MURASAME] What's
it matter to you?
This sword belongs
to my family,
which means I can do
whatever I want with it.
No, you cannot!
Hien was given to
me by our father and--
By our father, huh?
Wow, you've sure got
some nerve, guttersnipe.
You're not a real
member of our family.
Dad wrote me
off when he realized
I'd never be a
shinobi. That's fine.
But I'm not going to let
you take this sword from me.
I can't stand the
thought of a family heirloom
in the hands of
an outsider, like you!
If you hadn't been adopted,
Hien would've been mine someday.
It's all your fault! You
ruined everything for me!
I've always felt bad about
how everything worked out.
[MURASAME] What?
I totally understand
if you hate me,
but I never meant to hurt you.
[MURASAME] Yeah, right!
You're just trying to
make me look like a fool!
I swear I'm not doing
anything of the sort.
I simply want Hien back.
Then come here
and take it from me!
Damn!
Okay, now
you're askin' for it!
I took sixth place at
the chain-sickle tournament
back in grade school!
Look who's on lock down!
Let's see you
get out of this one!
I don't wanna
hurt you. Don't make me.
I'll show you!
[MURASAME]
How dare you mock me?
Goodbye, Brother.
How many times
do I have to tell you
not to call me that?
[MURASAME] I'll
never acknowledge you!
[MURASAME] I hate
that little bitch.
That sword is mine, and
I'm going to get it back!
[MURASAME] Who're you?
[HANZO] Nobody special.
Just an old man who's
kept an eye on you ever since
you first came to the school.
Your family's
worried about you.
Don't you think
it's time to head home?
No, I can't yet. Not
'til I get my sword back.
Now get lost!
[HANZO] If you leave now,
I will overlook your behavior.
I happen to be an
old friend of your dad's.
He told me that you're
not cut out to be shinobi,
but he's still proud
because you excel
at something else: business.
My dad said that?
You may not
be the best shinobi,
but I'm sure you'll be
a brilliant businessman.
[MURASAME] What's
your name, sir?
[HANZO] Trust me, it's
better for you not to know.
I'm just an insightful old man
who happened to be passing by.
[Hanzo chuckling]
♪
[IKARUGA] Get
it together, Asuka!
While your attacks
are extremely energetic,
they're completely
lacking in precision.
Got it!
Your punches
are about as strong as
a powder puff, Hibari!
Huh? Thanks!
That wasn't
meant as a compliment!
[HIBARI] Ah. Sorry!
Geez, what's with her?
Dunno.
[KATSURAGI] Alright,
what's wrong?
Nothing. I'm fine.
Then where the hell is
this attitude comin' from?
You're acting like a
frickin' drill sergeant.
I'm just trying to
help you guys, okay?
There's no telling when the
evil ninjas might attack us.
If we don't get
stronger we won't be able
to protect ourselves
against them.
I get it but yelling at
us isn't gonna do any good.
In fact, all you're
doin' is pissing us off!
You'd be singing
a different tune if
you had come face-to-face
with an evil ninja.
It's not my fault
you couldn't kick her ass!
[IKARUGA] If I
couldn't do it then
you wouldn't stand a chance!
Are you callin' me weak?
[IKARUGA] You're
not stronger than me!
[HIBARI] Uh-oh. I think
we should stop 'em, Yagyu.
[YAGYU] Everybody calm down.
Hey! Butt out first year!
[ASUKA] Check
it out, you guys!
[giggling]
Who wants futomaki rolls?
Grandpa was nice enough
to get up early and
make 'em just for us!
[all eating and giggling]
[IKARUGA] Her cheerfulness
makes us forget
we were ever fighting.
Sometimes I think
that she'd make a better
class chairman than me.
She has the power to bring
people together with a smile.
[HANZO] You've got it, too.
You just have a lot
on your plate right now.
[IKARUGA] Master Hanzo!
I didn't see you there.
As much as I love
my granddaughter,
I'm horrified by
her lack of skill.
You are the only
one who has the talent
and patience needed
to lead that unruly bunch.
Well, thank you, but
I'm so shaken up right now
that I'm not doing
a very good job.
I've got to get going
but would you do me a favor?
Please keep an
eye on Asuka for me.
I will.
Ikaruga, you're
doing a fantastic job as
class chairman, and as
the mother hen of this family.
Family?
[HANZO] What else
would you call it?
You girls laugh
together, cry together,
get angry with one another,
but at the end of the day
you still love each other.
I've never
thought of it that way
but you're absolutely right.
We may not be blood but
we're definitely family.
Thank you for pointing
that out to me.
No problem.
Besides, that means
there's one less thing
for me to worry about.
[gasp]
[all laughing]
Oh. Hey, Grandpa!
How's lunch? Are my
futomaki rolls any good?
[KATSURAGI] They're the best!
Yeah, so yummy!
[HIBARI] I love you and
your delicious futomaki rolls!
Master Hanzo.
[KIRIYA] You want to continue
her summoning art training?
[ASUKA] Who, me?
Yes. That is, if it's
all right with you, sir.
Um. I don't think
that's a good idea.
It's fine with me.
Uh... Hold on.
[IKARUGA] I think the
waterfall should suffice.
[ASUKA] Geez!
Slow down, Ikaruga!
[ASUKA] What's with
the cold-water ablutions?
[IKARGUA] In order to
successfully summon a creature,
you must first become
one with its environment.
And for frogs,
that would be water.
Uh. Okay!
[IKARUGA] Are you starting
to feel like a frog yet?
Yeah, I am. Now
that you mention it.
Good!
[screaming]
[HIBARI] Poor Asuka.
[KATSURAGI]
Think she can do it?
[YAGYU] She's
got a long way to go.
[Asuka screaming]
[ASUKA] I just can't do it!
I'm sorry but I can't touch 'em
let alone be chummy with 'em!
You'll never get over
your fear if you don't try.
[ASUKA] I really appreciate
your help, Ikaruga,
but I'm afraid
I'm a lost cause.
Well, I still
believe in you.
I don't give up on family.
We're a family?
Uh, just keep going, okay?
'Kay, I'll try again!
[ASUKA] Just a little farther.
Ahhh! Ikaruga, Help!
Ahhh!
[IKARUGA] Why don't
you just brush it away
with your other hand?
You make it sound
so easy but I'd feel bad
for the frog if I did that!
[IKARUGA] What do you mean?
Well, it'd be pretty
harsh if I slapped him away
and I don't wanna hurt
his feelings or anything!
I'm going to
pop over and see how
the others are doing.
I'll be back in just a second.
[ASUKA] Uh. Wait!
You're seriously gonna
leave me alone with this frog?
[IKARUGA] You can handle it!
It's cool. I'm not scared.
I lied! I'm totally scared!
[IKARUGA] Look out!
[screaming]
Gotta save the frog!
[Asuka] Huh?
Geez, Ikaruga! Why'd you
go and scare me like that?
Sorry, but it's
the only way I could
get you to
touch the little guy.
I thought he
was gonna be crushed
by that falling
rock so I rescued him.
You aren't scared
anymore, are you?
That's weird.
I'm not scared at all.
I dunno... why though.
But the more I look at him,
[ASUKA] he's kinda cute. I
can't believe I just said that.
I knew you'd be fine as
soon as you touched him.
You're the type who sees
the beauty in everything.
I am?
[ASUKA] 'Kay, here it goes!
[ASUKA] Secret Ninja
Art! Double Sword Slice!
I did it!
[KATSURAGI] That's awesome!
[HIBARI] Yeah, no kidding!
I must say I'm impressed.
That was flawless!
You did great!
Good work, Asuka.
Hey Grandpa! Pretty
good for my first time, huh?
[HANZO] Yep! I'm proud of you!
[KIRIYA] I would really
love to know what you did
to help her conquer her
fear of frogs, Ikaruga.
To be honest, it
wasn't all that hard to do
because she's a good person.
She'd convinced
herself that she was
afraid of frogs without
ever being around them,
so I just had to get
her to interact with one.
[IKARUGA] I made it seem
as though a frog was in danger
knowing that she'd save it.
Once she touched it,
her fear was gone.
[KIRIYA] That's amazing.
I'm so glad the girls
have you to help them.
You even put me to shame.
As class chairman, it
is my duty to assist you
with their training.
Master Hanzo. Thanks
for reminding me of that.
Don't be silly! I
should be thanking you
for going above and
beyond your duties.
I hope the girls realize how
lucky they are to have you.
You are so much more than
just their leader, Ikaruga.
You're like a
big sister to them.
A... sister?
[Hanzo chuckling]
[thunder]
Consider it done.
Yes, just leave them to us.
♪
[ASUKA] Isn't
this exciting, Hibari?
Training at the beach!
[HIBARI] Hooray!
[ASUKA] I wonder what
we're gonna do there.
[HIBARI] Don't let me forget
to bring my beach ball, okay?
[BOTH] We're gonna
have the best time ever!
[HIBARI] Jinx!
[ASUKA] Aw, man!
[HIBARI] Next time, "Seaside
Training - Shinobi Island".
[ASUKA] Come and get it
like your life depends on it!