♪
[NINJA] Hand it over!
[ASUKA] Crap, the scroll!
[NINJA] No, the
empty-shell technique?
[ASUKA] Ha ha! Fooled ya!
[Ninja gasp]
[Asuka grunt]
[Asuka gasp]
[ASUKA] Back off!
[ASUKA] You're askin' for it!
Man, that was so awesome!
[Asuka gasp]
[NARRATOR] Shinobi.
Mercenary agents who specialize
in unorthodox warfare.
Also known as ninja,
they're commonly hired
for covert operations
such as espionage,
infiltration,
and assassination.
[NARRATOR] Our tale follows
five shinobi-in-training
who've devoted their
lives to protecting Japan
from the forces of evil.
However, these aren't
your run-of-the-mill ninja;
they're beautiful
and buxom young ladies.
♪
[boat horn]
[ASUKA] I did it!
[ASUKA] I've taken the next
step toward achieving my goal.
[HANZO] You have yet to reach
your full potential, my child.
In order to gain true
power, you must use
both the katana
and the shield.
[ASUKA] The katana
[HANZO] Once
you've harnessed it,
you mustn't let it
corrupt you. Understood?
[HANZO] Go make me proud!
[ASUKA] Right! Grandpa,
I promise you that
I'm gonna be a first-rate
shinobi! You just watch!
[HANZO] Hmm.
Grandpa, I'll
do my very best.
I promise.
[ASUKA] Asakusa!
I'm finally home!
Wow! The city looks even
prettier than when I left!
[ASUKA] This is, like,
the best view ever!
[GIRL] Mine's not bad either.
So you're from Asakusa?
You did say you're
finally home, right?
Oh. Yeah, was I that loud?
Well, I don't think
the whole boat heard you,
but I did.
I'm so sorry I'm
just super excited
'cause I was going to
school here and I loved it
but something happened
and I had to leave for a bit
but now I'm back and, uh--
Sorry, I'll shut up now.
You're too cute.
I am?
[HOMURA] See ya!
[FEMALE ANNOUNCER]
Attention all passengers--
Wonder where
she goes to school.
[FEMALE ANNOUNCER] We'll be
arriving in Asakusa shortly.
♪
[NARRATOR]
National Hanzo Academy.
The school was established
in 1919 and currently has
about a thousand students.
Like any other
high school in Japan,
it's full of
perky teenage girls
and the teenage boys
who lust after them.
[BOY STUDENT 1] Whoa, check
out the hottie over there.
Never seen her before.
[BOY STUDENT 2] Wanna
go introduce ourselves?
[BOY STUDENT 1] Yeah!
What the--?
Where the hell'd she go?
She just disappeared.
[BOY STUDENT 11] That
sucks. She was really cute.
[ASUKA] Uh.
They think I'm cute?
I feel kinda bad
about ditching 'em,
but I need to stay
focused on my training.
Oh crap. I forgot.
[NARRATOR] However, there
is one thing that makes
Hanzo Academy different.
It holds a secret that
only a handful of skilled
and amply endowed
students know.
I made it just in time, huh?
[IKARUGA] Welcome back, Asuka.
[ASUKA] Thanks, Ikaruga.
I'm pumped and ready
to get back to training!
I'm glad you managed
to give those perverts
the slip earlier.
So, you saw all that, did ya?
Of course I did. You didn't
conceal your presence.
You should know
better than to run in
through the
school's front gates.
Guess I just got excited
'cause I've been away
for so long. [laughing]
While we're
technically students here,
our identities must remain
secret. Please be careful.
Don't blow our cover.
It won't happen again.
[KATSURAGI] Aw. Did
somebody get in trouble?
[ASUKA] Seriously, cut
it out! Let go, Katsu!
[KATSURAGI] How I've missed
your bodacious ta-tas!
Why do you insist
on fondling mine
when you've got your own?
A little groping
never hurt anybody.
Might even make 'em
grow a cup size or two.
I don't want 'em
bigger, in fact,
I wish they were smaller!
You would trade
these out for booblets?
[ASUKA] Yeah, in a heartbeat!
[crash]
[HIBARI] Ow, that really hurt.
You've gotta be the clumsiest
person I've ever met, Hibari.
I thought I was gonna
be late so I rushed over
as fast as I could but I
got stuck in the secret door
and dropped all my candy.
Huh? When did you
get back, Asuka?
This morning. I'm
fresh off the boat!
[HIBARI] So how'd you do? Did
you pass your advancement test?
[HIBARI] I'm so happy for you!
[ASUKA] I'm just
glad it's over!
[GIRL] Hibari, don't you
think you should be studying
for your own test
instead of celebrating
someone else's victory?
If Asuka can
pass it then I can, too!
Just wait. You'll see!
Where'd you come from?
I didn't even see ya there.
That's because I was
concealing my presence from you.
[laughing] Duh, I
totally knew that!
You're not gonna
let an underclassman
get the best of you, are ya?
Well, normally
no, but she's not
[ASUKA] your typical
underclassman. She outranks me!
That's 'cause Yagyu's
a shinobi prodigy!
[all scream]
It's time for class
to begin, ladies.
[IKARUGA] Good morning,
Kiriya-sensei.
[KIRIYA] Asuka.
Uh, yes, sir?
[KIRIYA] I hear
you passed your test.
[ASUKA] I did, but
it's really not a big deal.
[KIRIYA] Let's see
your scores. Hm.
"Narrowly avoided losing scroll
using empty-shell technique,
but uniform was severely
damaged in the process."
[KIRIYA] "Used a smoke
bomb in an urban area.
Finished with
no time to spare."
[chuckling] Well,
this is impressive!
[KIRIYA] You earned the lowest
possible passing grade
on your test. I've never
seen anything like it.
Seriously, it's
right on the line.
[ASUKA] At least
I passed, right?
True, I never said
that you had to ace it,
but I hope you'll shoot for
a higher grade next time.
Yes, sir!
[KIRIYA] Today you'll be
sparring against each other
to strengthen your
hand-to-hand combat skills.
Now get changed and meet
me in the training hall.
[coughing]
[KATSURAGI] I think
Kiriya-sensei's awesome and all
but I wish he'd lay
off the smoke bombs.
His methods
may be old-fashioned
but he's a great teacher.
Every shinobi's
got their own thing.
Guess his is smoke bombs.
Hmm. So, what's
your schtick, Asuka?
Lemme guess, you
suffocate all your enemies
with your big boobies!
[ASUKA] Leave me alone!
You're embarrassing me!
[KATSURAGI] Don't be embarrassed
of your tig-ol-bitties!
[IKARUGA] Quit goofing off!
We've got to get to training.
[ASUKA AND KATSURAGI]
Yes, ma'am.
Do we have to go?
[YAGYU] What's the matter?
[HIBARI] I'm just
scared, that's all.
I'm not good at
hand-to-hand combat, Yagyu.
[YAGYU] Hibari.
[HIBARI] Yeah?
You can do it.
Heck yeah!
If everybody's changed
and ready, then let's go.
Sensei will be
mad if we're late.
[horn]
[KIRIYA] All right,
today's first sparring match
will be between...
Katsuragi and Ikaruga!
[BOTH] Yes, sir!
[NARRATOR] The Cabinet's
Special Intelligence Bureau
Section One's top-secret
training center.
That was a mouthful.
Look, it's a
shinobi school, okay?
[NARRATOR] Third year
students, Ikaruga...
Got you!
[NARRATOR]
...and Katsuragi.
[Katsugari grunting]
Yeah! You go, Katsu!
[NARRATOR] Second year, Asuka.
[HIBARI] Now that's
what I'm talkin' about!
That was awesome!
[NARRATOR] First
year students, Hibari.
And the prodigy, Yagyu.
Next up, Asuka versus Yagyu.
Sir!
Here goes nothin'!
[NARRATOR] The only
people on campus who know
about this secret school
are the five top-heavy teens
in training and their sensei.
Together, they spend
their days and nights here
working towards their
goal of becoming shinobi.
[KATSURAGI] Still can't
believe I kicked your ass!
[IKARUGA] Only because
I couldn't use my sword.
Someone's a sore loser.
You just got lucky, okay?
[laughing]
Man. I'm gettin'
hungry. What do you guys
wanna do for lunch today?
I don't care as long as
it's not fast food again.
[ASUKA] I've got
it covered, ladies!
I brought you back a little
somethin' from my trip.
Wow, are those
Futomaki rolls?
They look so yummy!
I have to admit,
that's way better than
some silly souvenir.
These are delicious. Where
did you get them, Asuka?
I stayed at my folks'
last night and they wouldn't
let me leave
without taking some.
Right. How could I forget?
[IKARUGA] Your family
owns a sushi shop.
[ASUKA] The best in town!
What better way to
express my gratitude than
by caressing
your heavenly honkers?
[KIRIYA] Whoa. Are
those futomaki rolls?
Yeah! [coughing]
Would you like one,
Kiriya-sensei?
[KIRIYA] Why yes, thank you.
So tell me, Asuka, how's
Hanzo holding up these days?
[ASUKA] Grandpa?
Oh, he's doing great.
He wanted these rolls
to be perfect so he woke up
at the crack of dawn
this morning to make 'em.
You don't say. It's good
to hear he hasn't changed
even after all this time.
[KIRIYA] Enough
with the small talk.
It's time to take your shinobi
training to the next level.
I'm sending you on your first
mission outside the school.
Are you sure
we're ready for that?
Awesome! This is what
I've been waitin' for!
[NATSURAGI] What good're
all the shinobi skills
we've learned if
we never use 'em?
We finally get a chance
to show you what we can do!
Alright! Need us
to assassinate someone?
No, you'll be dealing with
punks in the shopping district.
The merchants are losing
business because of the
delinquents who're hanging
around and causing trouble.
So we have
to beat up punks?
I don't like punks.
They're scary.
No need to worry, Hibari,
I'll be right
there to protect you.
[Hibari gasps]
[KATSURAGI] Man, this
sucks. I thought we were
gonna get a cool
top-secret mission like
escorting a VIP or
infiltrating an embassy
for classified information.
Why would anyone
hire a group of students
for an important mission
of state when there are
plenty of qualified shinobi
available to do the job?
[KATSURAGI] If there's so many,
why're we huntin' punks?
How are we supposed to
fight 'em in a public place?
We'll be in big trouble if
anyone finds out we're shinobi.
[ASUKA] This might end up
being harder than we thought.
[IKARUGA] Yes, that's
why it's excellent training.
[KATSURAGI]
Yeah, yeah, whatever.
Are we just gonna wander
around 'til we find 'em
or should we come
up with a plan?
Hibari's got a good point.
We're wasting our time
walking around aimlessly.
I think we should split
up and search for our target.
[market chatter]
As far as I can tell,
the temple is punk-free.
[GIRL] 'Scuse me?
[ASUKA] Hey, I know you!
We met on
the water bus earlier.
You're stalkin' me, aren't ya?
[HOMURA] I'm on a
field trip with my school.
[ASUKA] Cool! How
do you like Asakusa?
It's beautiful but
I'd like it even more
if I could find my friends.
I got separated from 'em
and my stupid school
doesn't allow cell phones.
I don't suppose you remember
where you last saw 'em?
Uh, I think that it was
near one of the main streets.
[HOMURA] This
doesn't look right.
It's gonna be hard to
figure out what street it was
'cause Asakusa's
got so many of 'em.
Do you have any idea
where they might be headed?
I really appreciate
your help but I'm sure
you've got better
things to do.
Oh, it's not a big deal.
I don't have any plans today.
Are you sure?
'Cause you looked busy
when I ran into you.
Oh, no, I was
just wrapping up
a class assignment, that's all.
You go to school here, right?
I don't wanna get you
in trouble or anything.
Don't you worry,
that's not gonna happen,
I've got family
ties to my school.
I try not to abuse
it but it sure is handy.
Really? Well,
aren't you a lucky girl?
[HIBARI] Can I
ask you somethin'?
Why'd you come with me when
we were supposed to split up?
Because somebody
needs to protect you.
I'm not a baby, you
know, I can handle those
mean 'ol punks by myself!
You say that but what
if they sneak up on you?
Why would they wanna do that?
I know they're mean and all
but do they have to play dirty?
[GIRL PUNK]
Hold it right there.
Huh?
[Punks laughing]
[PUNK 1] Judgin'
by the uniforms,
these bimbos are
from Hanzo Academy.
[GIRL PUNK] Is that so?
One a them hoity-toity
schools, ain't it?
What does it matter to you?
'Cause if you go there,
you gotta have money.
You must be the punks that
we've been looking for.
Hibari! Send
out the signal, now!
[HIBARI] Okay!
[NARRATOR]
A shinobi smoke signal.
A warning shot into the sky that
only trained ninja can detect.
Basically, when
you see one of these,
you know shit's
about to go down.
I don't know where
they could've gone;
we've looked everywhere.
I'm sorry for the trouble.
Oh no, I'm sorry
I haven't been able
to help you find
your classmates!
[ASUKA] A signal!
Is something wrong?
Not at all.
Everything's A-OK!
I just realized
that we forgot to check
at the Benten-sama
shrine! C'mon, let's go!
Did you come here lookin'
for a fight, little girl?
I dunno if we can take
'em on our own, Yagyu.
We don't have to.
Great, more
Hanzo Academy chicks.
[Hibari small outcry]
'Kay, whose face
am I bashin' in first?
[PUNK] You startin'
a fight with us?
We've been asked
to rid the shopping district
of punks, like you.
I suppose that you could
just call us the
disciplinary committee.
Where's Asuka?
Have you seen her?
We could really use
her help right now.
[sigh] I wish she'd
take this seriously.
Can you handle crowd control?
Sure thing! Leave it to me!
If you want a
fight, then we'll give ya one!
[PUNKS] Yeah!
I guess we don't
have much of a choice.
Let's do this, Katsu!
Okay!
[ASUKA] Now I'm worried. I
hope the others are all right.
[HOMURA] We've looked
all over the city
and there's no sign of 'em.
They must've left already.
[ASUKA] You really think
they'd leave without you?
[Asuka startled]
[HIBARI] Sorry for
the inconvenience!
This road is temporarily
closed for construction!
Geez, I wish
they'd hurry it up.
I didn't even break a
sweat against those creeps.
I can't believe
Asuka never showed up.
Right? What're we
gonna do with that girl?
[Punks moaning]
[GIRL PUNK] Uh...
[KATSURAGI] How're those
scumbags getting back up
after we beat
the crap outta them?
Something's not right!
[IKARUGA] I get the feeling
we might be in over our heads.
Hey you guys, hold on!
What is it, Hibari?
It sounds crazy,
but I don't think
those punks have souls!
[gasp] What?
[GIRL] She may
not be the brightest.
But her senses
are sharp. [chuckles]
I'll do whatever it takes
to get my hands
on that little cutie.
No way! You
gotta be kiddin' me!
It's a shinobi kekkai!
[NARRATOR] A shinobi kekkai.
A barrier that
transcends time and space
where ninja can beat
the ever lovin' crap
out of one another
without being seen.
I knew I sensed something odd!
They're shinobi, too!
I didn't think it
would come to this.
[IKARUGA] But there's only
one thing we can do now.
Yeah, and that's
kick their punk asses!
Sensei's gonna be pissed
but we've got no choice.
[IKARUGA]
Shinobi transformation!
[HIBARI, KATSURAGI, AND YAGYU]
[NARRATOR] A
shinobi transformation.
A secret technique in
which ninja must release
dormant energy from
all six chakras at once.
If successful, they will
instantaneously change into
a uniform matching
their fighting style.
Not only does transforming
give us a quick peek
at the goods, if
you know what I mean,
but it allows them to use their
powers at the maximum level!
[Punks growl]
[HOMURA] Are you all right?
Uh. Yeah, I'm okay.
Thanks again for helping me.
[ASUKA] No problem. Uh sorry,
I don't know your name.
Mine's Asuka.
My name's Homura.
That's pretty, I like it!
Well, I'll see
you later, Homura!
[HOMURA] I blatantly
revealed my bloodlust to her
and she never even sensed it.
Don't worry, I'm
sure your friends will
turn up sooner
or later! Bye-bye!
Oh, I'm not worried. I
know exactly where they are.
[HARUKA] The time has come
my precious little puppets,
let's show these
girls what you can do.
[Girl Punk grunt]
[IKARUGA] They're wooden
dolls. But how can that be?
[HIBARI] Huh?
[KATSURAGI] We were attacked
by wooden dolls posing as punks.
How's that even possible?
[IKARUGA] I have no idea.
All I know is that
we were their target.
Who would attack us?
We don't have any enemies.
It's kinda hard to
explain but I only sensed
a single presence
from the dolls.
[HIBARI] It's as if one
person was controlling
all four of them.
Are you alright, dear?
I think so.
You're just as cute as can be.
Thanks?
[Haruka chuckling] See ya!
Wow! She's so
friendly and pretty!
[YAGYU] I don't trust her.
[HIBARI] Well,
I think she's sweet!
[ASUKA] There you are!
What happened to you?
Yeah, why's
your uniform soaked?
[ASUKA] It's kind
of a long story.
You see, this girl was lost
and couldn't find her class
so I helped her--
Whoa! You look pissed!
I am 'cause we needed
your help more than anyone!
Those punks we were after
turned out to be dolls.
[ASUKA] What do
you mean "dolls"?
We'll update you later.
It can wait until after
you've received your
punishment from Kiriya-sensei.
[ASUKA] My punishment?
[IKARUGA] You'd better be ready
for some hardcore meditation!
[ASUKA] Aw...
[HARUKA] They were quite
lovely. In fact, I'd like to
make all of them
my pretty, little puppets.
[GIRL] I'd like to hear
your thoughts, Homura.
Tell us about the legendary
shinobi's granddaughter.
[HOMURA] Let's just say I was
expecting a formidable warrior
and I left disappointed.
[GIRL 1] If they're so
weak, why're we waiting?
Let's go to Hanzo Academy
and take care of business.
[GIRL 2] It's obvious that
patience isn't your forte.
I think we should let them
stay blissfully ignorant
just a little while longer.
That way we can
go in for the attack
when they least expect it.
♪
[ASUKA] How do you stay so
focused during training, Katsu?
[KATSURAGI] Are you
sure you wanna know?
[ASUKA] Yeah!
[KATSURAGI] All I do
is think about squeezing
your breastsisis!
[ASUKA] I can't
believe I fell for that!
[KATSURAGI] Next time, "The
Legendary Shinobi Appears".
[ASUKA] Come and get it
like your life depends on it!