[distant dog barking]
[YAGYU] I'm
leaving now. Goodbye.
Okay.
♪
[knock knock]
Hey. It's me.
Are you still awake?
I wanted to apologize
for the way I acted earlier.
Hibari?
[ding]
♪
[alarm]
We have
intruders? But how?
Well, there's no
sign of any disturbance,
but just to
insure that it's safe.
Thank goodness.
[KIRIYA] No. It's a
knockout grenade. I can't--
They've stolen
the ninja art scroll?
What are we gonna do?
We've already tripled
our security details
since the break in occurred.
The problem is that the
measures we had in place
[KIRIYA] were so air tight,
that the only possible culprits
are the people
standing in this very room.
You don't honestly think that
one of us took it, do you?
I know it's harsh.
I don't like the sound
of it any more than you do.
Then who do you think
is the culprit, Sensei?
[KIRIYA] Forget it.
I don't want you to
concern yourselves with
this. Go wait in your rooms.
I'll call on you
when you're needed.
[HIBARI] Well, if I'm gonna
be stuck in here for the day,
I wonder what I should do.
I guess I could get
some reading done. Huh?
[HIBARI] What's that?
[HIBARI] "Super-secret
ninja art scroll."
Whoa! Why is this here?
I should go tell Sensei!
[HARUKA] Excellent work. I must
say, that was very impressive.
[HIBARI] No. It was you?
[HARUKA] Why do you
sound so surprised, cutie?
Don't tell me you already forgot
the promise we made last time?
We made a promise?
Please don't hurt her!
She was only
trying to protect me!
Aren't you adorable?
[gasp]
How could I ever say no to that
precious little face of yours?
I'll spare her
under one condition.
[HARUKA] All I ask is that
you promise to be my friend
from this day forward.
[HIBARI] Uh, what is this?
For you. It's a token of
our newfound friendship.
The earring!
You were an
adorable little puppet.
[HIBARI] Give it back!
I'm the one who'll be
doing the grabbing, dear.
So tell me. How does it
feel to betray your comrades?
You shouldn't worry.
They were treating you like an
incompetent child, after all.
But I see you for
what you truly are.
A talented shinobi
with unlimited potential.
[HIBARI] What do you mean?
[HARUKA] I could sense
it from the very first time
I laid eyes on you.
You're physically
weak, but your instincts
are all the
sharper because of it.
These abilities make you
perfectly suited for espionage.
[HARUKA] You have an
incredible talent, my dear.
But it's wasted here. If
you were at Hebijo Academy,
I guarantee that you
would feel appreciated.
Are you saying I should
become an evil ninja?
That's completely up to you.
[HARUKA] I'll be waiting.
I... don't know what to do.
Stop it, Yagyu. This is
Hibari you're thinking about.
There you are!
Something's happened!
Hibari's left us!
[ASUKA] I came to return
a book I had borrowed
and found that
letter lying on her bed.
No, I can't believe it.
Hibari betrayed the academy?
It's not like it was her fault.
[KATSURAGI] She was being
controlled by one of those
evil Hebijo skanks.
But... how
exactly did they do it?
[KIRIYA] With this.
An earring?
I knew it! A
psych-wave transmitter.
[NARRATOR]
A psych-wave transmitter.
Another convenient
piece of "ninja gear".
It is used to transmit the will
of a specially trained shinobi.
The person on the receiving end
is then completely controlled
by the user without
restraint. Kinky.
It is a trick often
used by puppet masters.
But when did they
manage to plant it?
[HIBARI] I'm so sorry.
This is all my fault.
I know that I might
never be forgiven
for the damage I've
caused Hanzo Academy.
But, no matter what happens
to me, I swear here and now
that I will get the scroll back.
Even if it costs me my life.
Hibari.
[KIRIYA] Yagyu!
[IKARUGA] You can't go alone!
[YAGYU] Shinobi Transformation!
Let's go!
Right!
[ALL]
Shinobi Transformation!
Yagyu!
I can't let
you go any further.
You think you can stop me?
I know you're upset,
but she could be anywhere!
If that means I search for
the rest of my life, so be it.
Stop it, Yagyu.
This won't help Hibari!
Just shut up and move!
[gasp]
You see her?
No, I don't think
she doubled back.
Leave it to the
squid-kid to go all
lone ninja when
Hibari needs help.
Last chance!
[YAGYU] She got behind me?
[Yagu struggling]
Just calm down and
think for a minute!
[YAGYU] Let me go!
Don't you care that
she's out there alone?
Listen to what you're saying!
She found her!
Don't let her go, Asuka!
Fine, I give.
This whole mess is my fault.
I knew... that Hibari
wasn't in her bedroom
last night, when
the theft occurred.
[KATSURAGI] You what?
When I heard about the
intruder, I remembered that.
But I couldn't bear the
thought of her betrayal.
So I-- I just
decided to ignore it.
And now we may have lost her.
None of us can
blame you for that.
You're just as much a victim as
she is. They tricked all of us.
Right! Nobody realized that
Hibari was being controlled.
There's nothing
we could've done.
[YAGYU] It's not just that.
During our
training, I got upset
and left her
alone on the grounds.
[YAGYU] I probably
made her feel guilty.
If only I had stayed with her.
Then maybe... she
wouldn't... have left us.
[ASUKA] You shouldn't
think like that, Yagyu.
It definitely isn't your fault.
So don't beat yourself up.
We're gonna bring her
back here safe and sound.
We'll retrieve the scroll
and teach those Hebi-hos
a lesson they won't forget.
If anyone should bear
the responsibility for this,
it's all of us.
We'll bring her home.
[IKARUGA] Because
we're all friends.
And that's what friends do.
They take care of each other.
We're friends?
Of course!
You're not the only one
who's worried about Hibari.
We want to do everything
we can to save her.
[birds chirping]
It's gotta be
around here somewhere.
[HIBARI] That must be it.
Hebijo Clandestine
Girl's Academy.
[EVIL NINJA 1] Who are you?
Um. I'm a student.
Please don't hurt me!
[EVIL NINJA 2] I've
never seen you before!
How do we know
you're not a spy?
I'm telling you
you've got it all wrong!
I was invited
here by Miss Haruka!
[EVIL NINJA 1] What?
[EVIL NINJA 2]
We'll see about that.
[EVIL NINJA] Miss Haruka.
Yes, go ahead.
[EVIL NINJA] We caught
a suspicious-looking girl
outside the academy.
[HARUKA] A girl?
[EVIL NINJA] She says
she was invited here by you.
[HARUKA] My, my. That
was sooner than I expected.
Have her brought to
my room immediately.
[EVIL NINJA] But the
rules say that when we
catch an intruder we must
report it to Suzune-sensei.
And I said you should bring
her to my room immediately.
[EVIL NINJA] Uh yes,
of course! Right away, ma'am!
Hello, cutie.
[HARUKA] Well, they
certainly weren't creative
with their knots, were they?
That's not very sexy at all.
My apologies. The girls
here may be a bit rough
compared to
what you're used to.
But I'm not like them.
I always take
special care of my pets.
[HIBARI] Is this alright?
[HARUKA] Of course it is.
I was just about to
bathe when you arrived.
Oh. I see.
[HARUKA] I'm so thrilled
that you've come here.
In time you'll learn to
think of it as your home,
and me as family.
Yeah. I can't thank you enough
for taking me in, Haruka.
[HIBARI] But
I'm a little worried
about how the
others will treat me.
Will they really accept
someone who was their enemy?
[HARUKA] Of course they will.
Don't you worry your
pretty little head.
Just relax and enjoy yourself.
Let me relieve
that troubled mind.
[HARUKA] I couldn't care
less about the headmaster
and his "secret
scroll" nonsense.
I already have
exactly what I wanted.
[HIBARI] I know I can do this.
I'm going to set
everything right, I swear it.
Welcome to the
elite training grounds.
Not much to look at, I know.
But you'll soon see we
use every resource we have
to make the workouts
as grueling as possible.
[HARUKA] Survival of
the fittest is law here.
[HOMURA] Well, well,
we have a visitor.
It appears that we've
lowered our standards,
guess they'll let
anyone in these days.
We're definitely gonna have to
talk to the security personnel.
Girls. I'd like you
to meet the newest member
of our academy. I
scouted her out myself.
[MIRAI] I swear, if
this is another one of your
"pet" projects,
I'm gonna throw up.
Are you sure about this?
Well, I don't have a
place at Hanzo anymore,
so I might as well
be somewhere I'm wanted.
I see. Well from now on consider
all of us your friends, okay?
[HOMURA] Something wrong?
Well, no. Just-- I didn't
expect you to trust me.
And why is
that? Shouldn't we?
Let me guess,
you think we're accepting
a former enemy too quickly.
What were you
expecting, a shake down?
Ever notice that "good"
people are often narrow minded?
Evil is a much more
tolerant way of life.
You might find
that the line between
good and evil is a blurry one.
Okay. But what
if I betrayed you?
Would you forgive me?
[HIKAGE] Depends. There are
many subtle levels of betrayal,
and as long as
you don't get caught
there's nothing
to forgive, right?
Uh.
If you think you
can get away with it,
then go ahead and try.
Evil never turns
its back on anyone.
[HOMURA] Just remember. Whatever
you do is at your own risk.
[MIRAI] Yeah, yeah. Anyway...
If you're stupid
enough to ignore me,
I'll slit your throat.
I won't ignore
you, just don't hurt me!
Uh huh. I've
heard that before.
So I'll be keeping
my eye on you, missy.
Uh. 'Kay.
So, I take it you're
a middle-class girl?
At least you're not a snob
like that one friend of yours.
May I ask you a question?
How do you feel about sprouts?
Huh?
Sprouts. I'm
talkin' about sprouts.
[HIBARI] Oh, um. They're
pretty good, I guess.
[YOMI] Really? Don't you think
that the government's increase
in the price of sprouts
is absolutely ridiculous?
I mean, how are the common
folk supposed to get by?
You understand me, don't you?
[HIKAGE] I like her already.
If she'll let
Yomi talk her ear off
she can be the head of
the team for all I care.
[HOMURA] Very funny.
It's almost time for
training to begin. Let's go.
[MALE TEACHER] The
word "shinobi" is written
as "heart" under "blade."
Temper your heart until it is as
cold as the steel of your sword.
Something wrong?
Oh, no. I'm just
surprised you have
so many students here.
I mean, Hanzo Academy only has
five students, including me.
That's because Hebijo
Academy isn't concerned about
[HARUKA] bloodlines
the way other schools are.
We gather here for a
variety of different reasons.
Some seek fortune,
while others simply
want to hide from the world.
[HARUKA] Homura came from
a family line of good ninjas.
If things had
played out differently,
she may have been
a classmate at Hanzo.
[HIBARI] Then, why did
she become an evil ninja?
[HARUKA] A matter of
"ineligibility," you could say.
As you may recall, one
of Hanzo's requirements
for new students
is that they have
no prior record
of criminal behavior.
[HIBARI] Criminal behavior?
[HARUKA] I heard
she stabbed someone.
[Hibari gasp]
[HARUKA] She
had no other choice
but to become an
evil ninja after that.
[HARUKA] Mirai, on the other
hand, was a victim of violence.
She joined Hebijo
Academy in order to
get revenge on
those that bullied her.
[HARUKA] Hikage was
raised on the battlefield
since she was a child,
which forced her to become
a ruthless and
deadly fighting machine.
[HARUKA] Yomi grew
up in extreme poverty,
and lost her
parents as a result.
She despises the
world's social structure,
and hopes to destroy it.
[HARUKA] Here at Hebijo
Clandestine Girls' Academy,
the five of us have been
recognized for rising to the
top of the class on the merits
of our own unique strengths.
[HARUKA] That freedom of
growth is what's allowed us
to become so powerful.
[HARUKA] That freedom of
growth is what's allowed us
to become so powerful.
[HIBARI] I miss my friends.
I miss Yagyu.
[HARUKA] Sorry to interrupt.
Huh?
This is Suzune-sensei.
She's advisor here
at Hebijo Academy.
[HIBARI] Hi. I'm Hibari!
[SUZUNE] Let's get to the
point. I find it unlikely that
you've switched
sides of your own accord.
You shouldn't worry.
It's not as though
this is without precedent.
[HARUKA] Now that these new
opportunities are open to her,
who knows how powerful
she might become?
Right dear?
[SUZUNE] Haruka.
I leave her to you.
[HARUKA] Yes, ma'am.
[SUZUNE] Hibari, was it?
[HIBARI] Uh, yes ma'am!
[SUZUNE] It takes
incredible resolve to turn
from good to evil.
You have to forsake
yourself, body and soul.
Body and soul, huh?
[HARUKA] Suzune-sensei
was once a good ninja,
just like you were.
That's top-secret, by the way.
I'm only telling you
because I want you to realize
you're not alone.
She could help
you if you'll let her.
That woman... used
to be a good ninja, too?
Hold on. Could
she possibly be--?
[MAN] A transfer?
Do you think that's wise?
[SUZUNE] One of our top
students recommended her.
She has significant
skills as a shinobi.
However, she is
a former member of--
[MAN] Administration
over new recruits is
your department, not mine.
[SUZUNE] Yes, of course.
[MAN] Tell me, are you
upset that I ordered the
theft of the scroll without
discussing it with you?
[SUZUNE] I don't
care either way, sir.
As I said before,
simply acquiring it
will accomplish nothing.
Without the chosen one,
it's just useless paper.
[MAN] Tread lightly, Suzune.
Who do you think
makes it possible
for you to even be here?
I'm the one who
took you in after you
failed your mission
for the good ninja.
You would be a corpse right
now if I hadn't intervened.
[SUZUNE] I would
never forget, sir.
[SUZUNE] Don't try to pretend
that you saved my life
out of the kindness
of your heart.
You've used me just
as much as I've used you.
The time has come.
Soon everything under
the moon and stars will
be stained with blood.
Apparently, Hebijo has
an abundance of students.
[IKARUGA] When you take
their numbers into account,
it'd be absolutely impossible
for them to stay hidden
inside the city
like Hanzo Academy.
Yeah, you got a point.
Maybe they hide in the
forest, or a mountain base.
So which way should
we start looking?
It's a shinobi facility,
so they probably
took chi flow and
feng shui into account
when they were
building the place.
[KATSURAGI] Mhm.
I can't keep up,
this is too complicated.
You seem to
have calmed down.
Please forgive my outburst.
[KIRIYA] I'm not the
one who deserves an apology.
I'm just glad Asuka
was able to find you.
[YAGYU] She
really surprised me.
[YAGYU] When she
confronted me, I was so angry
I couldn't hold back.
[YAGYU] Yet she
still managed to easily
dodge my full-powered thrust.
[YAGYU] Even the
Hebijo shinobi we fought
weren't able to
dodge that attack.
[KIRIYA] Asuka's
abilities do seem to be
improving at
an accelerated rate.
She's becoming quite powerful.
[YAGYU] Yes sir, I
believe that's the case.
[DAIDOJI] I can tell
there's a considerable amount
of untapped strength
deep within Asuka.
It's clear that she's yet
to realize her full potential.
Power like
hers that lies dormant
is an unconscious power.
As such, it is a
double-edged sword.
Should she
take the wrong path--
[KIRIYA] She'll end up
in the same place as her.
[distant bell jingle]
[YAGYU] What's wrong?
Nothing.
[KIRIYA] I have some
business to take care of.
Wait here until I get back.
Understood, sir.
Well, that was different.
[ASUKA] What are
you talking about?
He usually vanishes
with a puff of smoke.
Where's his ninja flair?
[KIRIYA] The sound came
from somewhere around here.
[bell jingle]
[KIRIYA] Huh? Who are you?
[SUZUNE] Hebijo Girls' Academy.
Shinobi Instructor. Suzune.
Suzune?
[SUZUNE] And you
are Hanzo Academy's
head instructor. Kiriya.
[SUZUNE] I challenge you.
Impressive. But I doubt you
came here just to show off.
[KIRIYA] Rin!
[chuckles] It's been awhile.
I had to see if you
had gotten rusty or not.
[SUZUNE] I would say the
answer is definitely "not".
[SUZUNE] I'm surprised
you didn't realize
it was me earlier.
I've had many great students,
it's hard to remember
each one's techniques.
[SUZUNE] I guess so. Speaking
of students, one of yours
just arrived
at Hebijo Academy.
Does the name
"Hibari" ring a bell?
Please tell me you haven't
done anything to her.
[SUZUNE] She's fine.
But we both have
responsibilities now, don't we?
I think you know
what you have to do.
Why did you do it?
Why did you choose
to become an evil ninja?
The answer to that question...
...is on the paper
you hold in your hand.
A map leading to Hebijo?
Well, what else did you expect?
I'll be awaiting
your arrival, Sensei.
No, wait!
♪
[MIRAI] How come everybody
ignores short people like me?
It pisses me off!
[HARUKA] I know a technique
that'll make people notice you.
[MIRAI ] Oh, really?
[HARUKA] You wear an ugly
man mask, carry a torch,
and then you hula dance
in the nude. It never fails.
[MIRAI] I just had
to ask, didn't I?
[HARUKA] Next time,
"Yin and Yang".
[MIRAI] Come and get it
like your life depends on it!