Come on! You can
do better than that!
You have to get in closer!
Yes, Sensei!
Vary your
moves so your opponent
doesn't catch you off guard!
Yes, sir!
I can't do this!
[KIRIYA] Stop
interfering, Yagyu!
Please don't be
upset with her, Sensei!
She's just trying to help me!
You're making
it worse, y'know.
What? I'm sorry.
That's enough!
If you think you're
somehow doing Hibari a favor,
you're gravely mistaken!
Alright girls.
You three are done for today!
You two stick around
for private training.
Aw...!
[all coughing]
That doesn't sound
like any fun at all.
I hope he's not
too rough on 'em.
I can't believe
he's punishing them
because Yagyu helped out.
Hibari's a shinobi.
[IKARUGA] She can't
keep expecting others to
come to her rescue.
Especially now.
[HIBARI] I promise I'll
do much better next time!
[DAIDOJI] I don't think
I've ever seen you train
your students with
such enthusiasm.
I didn't know
you were watching.
[DAIDOJI] Very impressive.
The five of them have unique
and versatile styles.
Finding them was a rare stroke
of luck on your part, Sensei.
[KIRIYA] Well, HQ can take
the credit for finding them.
All I do is train them.
And I couldn't do that if
it weren't for the efforts
of you and Master Hanzo.
As you know, the burden
of becoming true shinobi
is in their hands, not yours.
If they don't commit to it,
they will not survive this.
[KIRIYA] They have
certainly come a long way
since their arrival.
♪
Ladies, from this day
forward you are both shinobi.
Train hard and I will
guarantee your success.
Thank you, Sensei.
I look forward
to working with you.
Sounds like a blast!
Let's do this.
You're Ikaruga, right?
It looks like it's just
the two of us this year.
[KATSURAGI] My name's Katsuragi,
but you can call me Katsu, okay?
Pleasure to meet ya.
I don't see any need
for further conversation.
So, that's the way you
wanna play this? Fine then!
[KIRIYA] First let's assess
what kind of skills you have.
[KATSURAGI] Yes, sir!
[IKARUGA] Sir.
Oh, please.
This should be easy.
Wait 'til I get
my hands on her.
Now begin!
You think you're so slick.
[crash]
[KIRIYA] That's enough!
[Katsuragi breathing heavy]
Damn you!
I can't believe I
didn't hit her once.
Nimble little ice queen.
Wait. You can't get
discouraged now, silly.
[KATSURAGI] You've got
a dream to catch, remember?
[KATSURAGI] I'll beat
Miss bob-cut somehow.
Mine are bigger!
Hey, it wouldn't
kill ya to crack
a smile sometimes,
mosquito bites.
[IKARUGA] Smile, she says?
[IKARUGA] I don't have
the right to smile.
Katsuragi.
Recite the five
fundamental elements for me.
Right, uh. Let me think!
They are as follows:
fire, earth, metal,
wood, and water.
[IKARUGA] These
elements are crucial
in mastering shinobi techniques.
Good.
Show off.
Tryin' to rub
my nose in it, huh?
Okay I'm big enough to
admit when I've been beaten.
You may be able to
wipe the floor with me now
but one day I'll be
a lot stronger, just wait.
That stuck up little bitch!
[Katsuragi power yell]
Wow, you're
nimble in the morning.
Yeah, well, you're annoying
at any time of the day.
Whaddya say we
forget about training for
a moment and see who comes
out on top in a real battle?
[KATSURAGI] If you've got
a problem why don't you say
it to my face!
I'm here to become
a great shinobi.
I have no need
for distractions.
Oh really?
If that's all I am,
then I'll play the part.
Oh, pardon me!
[KATSURAGI]
Catch ya later, bob-cut!
Those legs of yours
just don't quit, do they?
And your boobs are so big
they have their own zip code!
Mind if I pay a visit?
Do you enjoy being
a thorn in my side?
You finally gonna
do something about it?
It's not like you're
giving me any option.
Shinobi kekkai!
Huh?
[IKARUGA] No one will
interfere with us in here.
Are you insane?
Kiriya-sensei told us not
to use this outside of practice
or we'd be in big trouble!
[IKARUGA] That's funny.
You didn't care about
the rules before.
Are you all talk
and no substance?
Or is there actually a
little bit of fight in you?
Why don't you come
over here and find out?
Just fight me for real!
Very well, if
that's what you want.
What the hell?
As if your arrogance
wasn't bad enough,
you also tried
to barge into my life.
People like you
really piss me off!
Ha! Glad to hear it!
[Katsuragi power yell]
It's about time you
showed me how you feel.
You actually like
hearing that I want
nothing to do with you?
Well, it's better
than being fake
and pretending
to be my friend?
Remember you're not blood; you
were brought into this family.
[MURASAME] Don't
get too comfortable
'cause you don't belong here.
[IKARUGA] I have to
become the strongest.
Why bother?
You know nothing about me!
I can say the same to you.
At least I tried
to break the ice.
[GIRL STUDENT 1]
She's fighting again?
[GIRL STUDENT 2]
Her family left her.
And with the way she acts,
I can see why they did.
[KATSURAGI] I won't be beaten.
[Katsuragi power yell]
[Ikaruga power yell]
The kekkai is
starting to collapse?
That's impossible!
Not good.
I guess we better
get outta here.
No. I can't release it!
But you're the
one who made it!
Maybe you're
not doing it right!
I don't know another way!
What's gonna happen to us
if you can't bring it down?
What do you think will happen?
We'll be stuck inside with
no hope of ever escaping.
Well, that sucks.
We could be stuck in here
until we're skin and bones.
This barrier is going
to become our grave.
That's not gonna happen.
Katsuragi. I--
We're gonna get outta here
but we have to work together
to make that happen, okay?
Together?
Follow my lead,
and start kicking
like a crazy person.
Are you really not
afraid or just faking it?
I'd be a piss poor shinobi
if I let death bother me.
[KATSURAGI] If I can escape,
great. If not, oh well.
You don't blame me
for trapping you in here?
You crack me up, Ikaruga.
Why would I blame you for
something you couldn't control?
Huh?
It sounds like you're
asking for blame.
And that can be
a rough burden to carry.
[KATSURAGI] Shit happens.
Just work to make it right.
[KATSURAGI] I think I've
finally figured you out.
[IKARUGA] What?
In a way, you and
I are pretty similar.
What do you mean?
We both have a tendency
to be total klutzes.
Maybe that's
why we butt heads.
We see the same things in each
other that we try to hide
from everyone else in the world.
[KATSURAGI] So we lash out,
act childish, and
become social shut-ins.
We let our insecurities
take hold and we
end up sabotaging what could've
been a kick-ass friendship.
Oh, Katsuragi. I'm sorry.
Well, that's not
coming down anytime soon.
Ikaruga?
If we give up we might
as well be dead, right?
Yeah. Whaddya
say we show this wall
what two shinobi can do?
Sounds good to me.
Let's get freaky.
[both power yell]
[crash]
[KATSURAGI] Kiriya-sensei!
I seem to recall
forbidding you from creating
a kekkai barrier
outside of practice.
Wait. How did you bring it down?
I thought only
I could do that!
A better question would be
why you did it
in the first place.
[KIRIYA] As punishment,
you'll wait out
in the hall until sunrise.
[KATSURAGI] Wait, sunrise?
But it's just now sunset!
[KATSURAGI] This is a little
excessive don't ya think?
I didn't-- I'm sorry.
For what? Doesn't bother me.
I get some exercise and
I get to watch the star pupil
let it all hang out.
Just don't tell anyone!
Well, anyway.
I hope we get some new
students at the school soon.
Hell yeah.
The more friends we have,
the more fun it will be.
Yes, I agree.
[IKARUGA] Friends.
[KATSURAGI] I hope
we get a girl who's more
grope-worthy
than somebody I know.
Hey! Are you implying
that I'm subpar?
Well, honestly, your
shino-boobs could be bigger.
[birds chirping]
[IKARUGA]
Shinobi Transformation!
Well done, Ikaruga.
That was a flawlessly
performed technique.
This state reflects your
inner self and amplifies
your strength to its
full potential in battle.
Wow, I like
your "inner self".
Stop. Don't
look at me like that.
Katsuragi! Show us your stuff.
You got it, boss!
Time for your shot, big boy.
Hey! What kind of stupid
transformation is that?
I've always wanted
to cosplay a nurse.
Don't you think I look hot?
Would you please get serious?
Technically there
aren't any rules restricting
that type of clothing that--
Kiriya-sensei!
[KIRIYA] Katsuragi.
Your clothing choice
should allow for
mobility in combat.
That outfit is hardly suited
for strenuous activity.
Then I'll try again!
[KATSURAGI]
Shinobi Transformation!
This should be easier
to kick some ass in, huh?
Oh no you don't!
I refuse to fight alongside
someone dressed like that!
[KATSURAGI] You are
such a Debbie-downer.
[KATSURAGI] Well,
I guess this should do it.
The two of you have
worked incredibly hard
this past year, and your ability
to transform is proof of that.
Please help your underclassman
achieve the same results.
[BOTH] Underclassman?
[ASUKA] I'm gonna be late
on the very first day!
Here it is!
[ASUKA] Okay so I go
through this tearoom.
Or maybe it was--?
Ahhh!
[KIRIYA] Welcome.
As you may have
guessed, this young lady
is Hanzo Academy's
newest student and she'll be
training with you from now on.
My name's Asuka!
A big-boobed newb!
That's just what
I was hoping for!
Don't start molesting
her on the first day.
[KIRIYA] Incidentally, Asuka
is also the granddaughter
of Master Hanzo.
She's the granddaughter--
Of the legendary shinobi?
Yeah. It's a pleasure
to meet you both.
[ASUKA] Ahhh!
That didn't go so well.
[KATSURAGI] I guess being
legendary isn't hereditary.
Maybe she's just nervous.
[IKARUGA] Perhaps.
She puts on a good show.
I think she'll
fit in just fine.
I guess.
[KATSURAGI] You've got
a lot of bruises.
You gonna be okay there, newbie?
[ASUKA] Oh yeah, you bet!
This is nothing!
[KATSURAGI] So
there's a warrior's heart
behind these fun bags!
Ahhh!
Hey, what do you
think you're doing?
Giving those bruises some TLC.
Huh?
[ASUKA] Somehow I don't
think that's going to heal them
any faster! I'm through
bathing. Goodnight!
I think I found
a new groping buddy.
She's nothing like us.
Great things are
expected of that girl.
I'm sure success will be handed
to her on a silver platter.
[IKARUGA] Especially
because of her grandfather.
Her life must be easy.
I don't believe it.
Are you jealous of her, Ikaruga?
[KIRIYA] Asuka! You
have to pick up the pace!
[ASUKA] Right!
[IKARUGA] I was resented
for showing even a glimpse
of my talent back home.
She is attending the
finest shinobi school
in the country and still
can't manage to show any?
[ASUKA] Ahhh!
[KATSURAGI] Asuka!
Asuka, don't come any closer!
[KIRIYA] Be thankful
this was just training
and not the real deal.
I'm sorry about that, you guys.
Yeah, yeah, no worries.
[KIRIYA] Asuka, where did
those clothes come from?
[ASUKA] What happened?
I wasn't wearing this earlier.
Wait a minute, this is
the really nice looking
school uniform I saw the
other day! That's so weird!
[IKARUGA] Did she unconsciously
trigger a Shinobi Transformation
with no effort at all?
[ASUKA] I can't
do anything right.
You gotta be kiddin' me.
We went through a
whole year of training
before we were
able to transform.
Well, I doubt I'll
be able to do it again.
To be honest, I don't
have the slightest clue
how I even pulled it off.
[IKARUGA]
Still. You have talent.
Of course she does, silly.
She's the granddaughter
of Master Hanzo.
You say that, but I
don't feel like I'm doing
his name any justice.
I have to succeed, not
just for the sake of Grandpa,
but for myself. I'm
gonna try my very best.
That's my path.
Asuka.
Keep up that
attitude and I guarantee
victory will be yours!
[ASUKA] You think so?
[IKARUGA] I see. So
she is like us, after all.
Well, that settles it.
From this day on, I'm gonna
think of you as my big sisters!
Huh?
You inspire me
and you've already
helped me out so much!
[ASUKA] That's what big sisters
do! I hope you don't mind.
[KATSURAGI] Nope! Not as
long as I get to grope you.
[ASUKA] Okay! What?
[ASUKA] A squid?
That's incorrect.
It's a flying squid.
[ASUKA] Huh? Oh, you don't say.
I would like to welcome
our newest students,
Yagyu and Hibari.
It's nice to meet you.
Hi. I hope that we can
all become good friends.
Aw, they're both
absolutely precious!
And now that they're here, I'm
not gonna be the newbie anymore!
[KIRIYA] Excellent work!
Whoa.
She hasn't
even had any training
and she's already amazing!
Most impressive.
This should be interesting.
Someone please
get me out of here!
[KIRIYA] Come on!
[IKARUGA] Then there's her.
[ASUKA] Well, at least she's
still managing to avoid them.
[KIRIYA] Stop running away,
You should be dodging!
[HIBARI] But I don't understand
the difference, Sensei!
[HIBARI] It's finally over.
You've got some wicked skills.
Hey!
[IKARUGA] Stop right there!
It's an underclassman's duty to
clean up before leaving class!
[HIBARI] Yagyu.
That one has some
kinda nerve, doesn't she?
Skill means
everything to a shinobi.
Huh?
Therefore the ones
with the least skill should
be sweeping the floors.
[IKARUGA] Don't
walk away from me!
You can't ignore the rules just
because you feel like it!
[KATSURAGI] Don't
blow a fuse, Ikaruga!
[IKARUGA] Look at me
when I'm talking to you!
As class chairman, I
should not have to tolerate
that kind of impertinence
from a junior student.
Guess things are
gonna heat up around here.
I'm sure that she's
really a nice person though.
At least she gets along
really well with Hibari.
[KIRIYA] Things were
rough for a while.
But Yagyu was eventually
able to break out of
her "problem child" phase.
Then again they're
all problem children.
And that includes you as well.
Daidoji, graduate and get
outta of my hair already.
Nah. I have way too
much fun annoying you,
and you know that I
have something to finish
before I can leave.
[fighting]
[Daidoji heavy breathing]
Keep on training, Daidoji.
You'll beat me someday.
I'll be graduating
before long but...
I will score a hit
on you before that day!
[RIN ] Well, best of luck.
I know you can do it.
I won't be holding back,
so give it your all.
You can count on it.
However, before I
could fulfill my promise,
[DAIDOJI] she...
I should never have let
her go on that mission.
But she managed
to talk me into it.
[RIN] Didn't you
say this assignment was
imperative to the state?
You know I'm the best choice for
the job, so please let me go.
You're incredibly skilled,
but you just recently
graduated and
it's far too dangerous.
You have to let me do this!
Let me prove to you that
I can be a super-ninja!
[KIRIYA] I should
have stopped her.
If I had a
stronger will maybe
she'd still be with us today.
I have a feeling she
would have gone no matter
what you decided in the end.
[KIRIYA] This war with Hebijo
Academy is going to be
a difficult one.
They'll regret
ever crossing us.
It's up to me to
set everything right.
The end is approaching,
and who knows.
Perhaps my graduation
isn't as far away as I thought.
[Hibari and Yagyu struggling]
I'm sorry.
It's all my fault
that you're out here.
I'm the one who
should apologize to you.
[HIBARI] Huh?
[KIRIYA] If you think you're
somehow doing Hibari a favor,
you're gravely mistaken!
Hey, are you all right?
[YAGYU] I'm
leaving now. Goodbye.
Okay.
[SUZUNE] So, you ignored my
recommendation and gave orders
to Haruka without informing me?
[MAN] Seizing Hanzo Academy's
secret ninja art scroll
is the most crucial mission.
[SUZUNE] The scroll itself is
useless without its chosen one.
That's why I didn't
recommend its retrieval.
[SUZUNE] The best course of
action would be to allow one of
their members to develop
into the chosen one.
After that, we turn
them to our side.
It's a simple yet
effective strategy.
[MAN] We could train a
chosen one of our own liking
after we've taken it.
[SUZUNE] That would be unwise.
We have yet to properly train a
chosen one for our own scroll.
[MAN] I want results, Suzune.
I've grown tired of waiting.
And besides...
it's already too late.
♪
Is that--? Hm.
[HIBARI] I thought
I left that on my desk.
[HIBARI] Yagyu
seemed really angry.
I don't blame her.
She's probably tired of
protecting me all the time.
I wonder if I'm always gonna
be such a burden on everybody.
[HARUKA] It's time to
call in that favor, cutie.
Is that okay with you,
my precious little puppet?
♪
[YOMI] I can't
believe it, Hikage!
We finally get the
chance to do a preview!
[HIKAGE] Woo hoo.
[YOMI] I would like to take
this opportunity to express
the true majesty of sprouts!
[HIKAGE] Um, Yomi?
[YOMI] Yes?
[HIKAGE] We don't
have time for that.
[YOMI] But--
[HIKAGE] Next time, "Hebijo
Clandestine Girls' Academy".
[YOMI] Come and get it
like your life depends on it!