[NARRATOR] The Hebijo
Clandestine Girls' Academy.
They embrace the
philosophy that evil is more
magnanimous than good.
It's a secret training institute
of darkness with the objective
of raising evil ninjas.
Sexy, well-endowed,
evil ninjas.
[MIRAI] I wonder what
this meeting's about.
You think she wants us to
go mess with those losers
from Hanzo Academy again?
[HOMURA] Ha. Maybe.
[MIRAI] If we do
get sent back there,
I hope we get to do
some damage this time.
[GIRL NINJA] Ahhh!
[girl ninja wimpering]
[GIRL NINJA] I'm so sorry!
I'm so sorry!
Please forgive me!
[wimpering]
You're gonna have to
try harder if you wanna be
a shinobi someday.
[MIRAI] Do better next time.
Thanks. I will!
[MIRAI] That poor girl, her
skills are mediocre at best;
she doesn't stand a chance.
[HOMURA] It's not like you
to offer words of encouragement
to another student, Mirai.
[MIRAI] The more hope one feels
while trying to succeed,
the greater their sorrow
will be in failure.
[both chuckle]
Well, you're just as
vindictive as ever, aren't you?
Huh?
[gasp]
[HOMURA] Hebijo Girls' Academy
Rule Number Forty Eight.
"At all times on campus,
a jonin is obligated to answer
the challenge of a genin,
regardless of circumstances."
[girl ninja nervous]
You've certainly
got nerve, don't you?
But as brave as you are,
attacking me is the single,
biggest mistake
you've ever made.
[girl ninja gasp]
Huh?
Ahhh!
[YOMI] I'm so incredibly
perturbed right now.
What's the matter, Yomi?
The rich refuse
to share their wealth
as the poor's quality
of life dwindles.
Yeah. But that's not
exactly a new development.
If rich people want
to pay through the nose
for expensive food and
vegetables that's fine with me,
but the poor shouldn't
have to do that.
Yeah...
They've raised the
prices on low-cost produce,
[YOMI] including sprouts, which
is basically all they eat.
It's not fair.
[HIKAGE] What can ya do?
Hey, are you even listening
to what I'm saying right now?
[HIKAGE] No, not really.
I didn't think so.
[HARUKA] Well,
it's just about time.
If you'll excuse me.
[HIKAGE] Crap.
Is it that late already?
Hikage. Wait up,
where are you going?
Don't you understand the
powers--
[HIKAGE] I'm more concerned
about getting chewed out
than I am about
over-priced produce.
[YOMI] I was talking!
[HIKAGE] C'mon, let's go.
Man. Oh well, what's the use?
[WOMAN] There's only one reason
I've called you together.
Brand new orders have
come down from the top.
[HOMURA] From the Headmaster?
♪
[Hibari yelling]
[YAGYU] Keep going,
don't give up yet!
[HIBARI] Uh.
Oh. I think I need to take
a little break first, Yagyu.
Do you think your enemies
will give you a break?
I'm so scared!
What if those evil shinobi come
back and try to murder us?
[YAGYU] There's no
reason to be scared.
'Cause if they do...
I'll defend you.
Awe...!
[KIRIYA] Hibari, get up!
Back on your feet right now.
Shinobi do not take breaks!
Evil ninja are not going
to wait for you to rest.
[HIBARI] Sorry.
[KIRIYA] They claim
to be students
from Hebijo Girls' Academy.
But why would they repeatedly
take provocative action
without killing any one?
[KIRIYA] We still have no idea
what their objective is.
But there's one thing
we can be certain of.
We have to train.
We have to work hard enough so
that when we meet them in battle
a second time, we have
the strength to defeat them.
Wow, Katsu! You
sure are training hard.
You're amazing!
[KATSURAGI] There's no telling
when those Hebijo tramps
are gonna strike again.
But I wanna make sure I'm ready
to take 'em on whenever they do!
[ASUKA] Whoa.
And I didn't think she
could get much stronger
than she already was. Ahhh!
Ugh.
[HIKAGE] You're even
weaker than I thought.
[KATSURAGI]
I won't be defeated!
I'll train hard.
I'll get stronger!
I swear, I'll do
whatever it takes!
[girls grunting]
[YOMI] They have everything
their hearts desire
and yet they still bellyache.
It's as if they don't realize
how privileged they are,
as if they're entitled
to such largesse.
These stuck up rich kids
make me sick to my stomach.
But we'll teach them
a lesson, won't we?
[chuckle] When they
become our little puppets,
we can train them
however we like.
It really is a shame
that I'm not allowed
to do anything to them.
[HOMURA] First things first,
we need to search the campus
and figure out where the
good ninja are training.
[MIRAI] Why would they
intentionally put a shinobi
training center in the middle
of a college-prep school?
This is gonna be
a big pain in the butt!
[HOMURA] I suppose
it makes sense.
Hide a tree in the forest,
hide a student in a school.
But now that you mention it,
they sure seem to enjoy doing
everything in a roundabout way.
Well, I couldn't care less
about how they do things
as long as we're able to
outsmart those goody-goodies.
[WOMAN] The girls have
successfully infiltrated
Hanzo Academy, sir.
[MAN] They are Hebijo
Clandestine Academy's finest.
Infiltration should
be easy for them.
The only question is--
[WOMAN] Yes.
The location of their
hidden training facilities.
As well as the super
secret ninja art scroll
that lies within it.
[MAN] Are you absolutely
certain that's where
the scroll can be found?
[WOMAN] There
can be no mistake.
[MAN] It is not
that I doubt you.
In fact, it's because
this intel came from you
that I feel assured.
[WOMAN] Thank you.
[MAN] However, the
existence of the evil ninja
is deeply hidden in darkness.
Acting out in the open risks
exposing that darkness
to the light of day.
[WOMAN] The girls are
well aware of that, sir.
They will exercise discretion.
[MAN] Good.
I have high
expectations, Suzune.
[SUZUNE] Yes, sir.
[KIRIYA] Ninjitsu has always
been a skill of the mind.
The body is just an extension.
However, if you pair a strong
mind with a capable body,
true skill will
start to show itself.
In other words, it's by
standing firmly with both feet
on the ground and a focused
mind that the earth will become
your strength, got it?
Uh, yeah, I understand!
[KIRIYA] Katsuragi!
Huh?
What's goin' on, is it
time for lunch already?
[BOTH] She's in trouble.
[KIRIYA] Yes, she is!
Now, go out in the hall!
[HARUKA] We've searched
the entire campus.
This is the only
possibility left.
[YOMI] It's much older and less
lavish than the other buildings.
[HOMURA] And it's
not in use anymore.
It's probably still here
for historical purposes.
[MIRAI] "Off-limits to
unauthorized personnel," huh?
Yeah.
It looks as though we've found
their secret hideout, ladies.
[MIRAI] I can smell
good ninja and it reeks!
Man.
Why'd he have to send me out
in the hall for taking a nap?
[KATSURAGI]
That's not cool at all.
And it's such a
beautiful day outside.
I'd rather be out there
playin' and havin' fun
than stuck inside
this hell hole.
[KATSURAGI] Yeah.
Like when I was a kid.
Those were the days.
[Young Katsuragi laughing]
Choco!
[laughing]
[YOUNG KATSURAGI] Wait!
Mommy! Daddy!
[Choco barking]
[NARRATOR] When
Katsuragi's parents failed
an important mission,
they knew that according to
shinobi law, the only way
they could ever make up
for their failure,
would be to surrender
their lives.
Instead, they chose to
disregard the law completely
and went on the run to
live as fugitive ninjas.
They left their
young daughter behind
so she would not be
implicated in their crimes.
[crying]
[NARRATOR] Katsuragi believed
that if she worked hard
to become a superior good ninja,
her parents' crime and flight
would eventually be forgiven.
[YOUNG KATSURAGI]
Someday I'll be reunited
with Mommy and
Daddy, I know it!
I just have to get strong!
Stronger than
any other shinobi!
[KATSURAGI] Not again.
I told myself I wasn't going
to think about them anymore.
This sucks.
[Hikage sigh] I don't
understand why we're waiting.
Can't we just bust in?
If this really is their
secret headquarters
I doubt getting inside will
be as easy as "bustin' in".
What do you
suggest we do, Haruka?
[chuckles] Well, first off
we'll need to eliminate
the most dangerous
obstacle in our way.
[HOMURA] We have a
mission. We're not here to
run around in circles.
There's no need to worry.
They'll be stripped bare soon
enough, I can promise you that.
[Haruka chuckling]
[alarm]
Oh wow! That's so loud!
It's all right!
Somebody's triggered
the intruder alarm.
Intruders?
Oh no!
[KIRIYA] They appear
to be ordinary students.
How can you be sure?
So there's no need to worry?
Hey, sensei.
Did those
idiot jocks sneak over
and trip the friggin'
alarm again?
[KIRIYA] It would appear so.
[KIRIYA] Katsuragi,
that's enough.
You may return to class now.
Yes, sir.
Thank you, dumb jocks!
I dunno who you are but
because of your stupidity,
I'm off the hook!
[cawing]
[KIRIYA] What are
you doing in here?
[KIRIYA] Surely you two
know this area's off-limits
to students, don't you?
Let me guess, you little
punks are playing hooky?
One of you wanna say something?
[KIRIYA] You'd better
start talking or else.
Your classes
and names, please.
If you won't tell me, I'll
have to march you straight
to the faculty office myself.
[KIRIYA] Huh?
They're puppets?
No, the girls!
What the hell?
Something is wrong!
Ikaruga, can you
tell what's going on?
It's a shinobi kekkai!
What? But how?
No. Yagyu, don't go!
[KATSURAGI] Yagyu?
[HIBARI] Please, come back!
It's too dangerous!
Let's go!
[IKARUGA] Is it
just this building?
No.
The entire academy has been
enveloped in a shinobi kekkai!
[KATSURAGI] This is insane!
How could one person
put up a barrier this big?
[IKARUGA] I don't
think this is one person.
The only explanation is that
a group of shinobi each raised
a barrier at the same time
and then combined them!
I didn't even know
that was possible.
I've never seen it
with my own eyes before
but I've read books about
shinobi who have the ability
to pull it off.
And I remember...
one of them
was puppet masters.
You mean like the
one who attacked us?
[HIBARI] That was
the scariest thing
that's ever happened to me.
I bet those shinobi from Hebijo
Girl's Academy are behind this!
Yeah, and I suspect
they're the ones who
tripped the alarm earlier.
[KATSURAGI] 'Cause they
wanted to separate us
from Kiriya-sensei!
[KIRIYA] Damn it!
An evil ninja sneak attack!
Be careful. The evil
ninja are here somewhere
merging their kekkai barriers.
We have to stop them fast.
If we don't figure out a way
to pull them apart, somehow,
then we're sitting ducks.
They wanna go "fist-a-cuffs"?
Well, that's just fine by me!
I'm so scared.
No, don't be. 'Cause
I'll always protect you,
no matter what.
Everybody, prepare
for battle, now!
[IKARUGA] Shinobi
Transformation!
[ASUKA] Shinobi Transformation!
[KATSURAGI] Shinobi
Transformation!
[YAGYU] Shinobi Transformation.
[HIBARI] Shinobi Transformation!
[KATSURAGI] Come out, come out,
wherever you are!
Well? Dontcha wanna play?
Wait, Katsuragi!
What the hell's your problem?
We're inside the
enemy's shinobi kekkai.
It's dangerous to recklessly
charge ahead like that.
Not as dangerous as sittin'
around waiting to be attacked!
I agree, but first we need to
know what the enemy's doing!
[chuckles] And now it's time
to get this party started.
Heads up you guys!
Ugh!
[evil ninjas worried]
[Katsuragi power yell]
[Ikaruga power yell]
Stay away from me,
you big dummies!
[ASUKA] Hey wait. Where am I?
What the heck happened?
And where did
everybody else go?
She disappeared!
Help me, Yagyu!
What the--?
Hibari!
[IKARUGA] I should've
seen this coming.
How could I be so stupid?
Those puppets were just
decoys used to divide us.
[Yomi chuckling]
You upper class
girls are so gullible.
If you let me out of
this kekkai right now,
I won't hurt you.
You're in no position
to be making threats.
So you stole a uniform.
And then you
infiltrated the academy.
That was a bold move.
Well, I can't say
I'm a fan; just the thought
of how much a uniform like this
must cost makes me wanna puke.
What do you want?
Why are you and
your comrades here?
Oh, the entitlement
of a rich kid.
It never ceases to amaze me.
I'll tell you, even though I
don't appreciate your attitude.
But I'm not going to say a
word unless you can defeat me.
[YOMI] Shinobi Transformation!
[chuckles]
[Yomi power yell]
I can't believe
how powerful she is!
I won't be able
to last much longer.
Aw, are you getting
sweaty because of our fight?
I'd hate to mess up your hair,
you privileged brat!
[IKARUGA] Ahhh!
I've gotta find Hibari!
I swore I would protect her!
And I swore I would
defeat you the next time
we met in battle.
[MIRAI] Shinobi Transformation!
Ugh.
[MIRAI] Don't run away yet!
I'm just gettin' started!
Hibari, I promise
I'm coming for you!
You get your
ass back here now!
Why don't you stop with
the games and show yourself?
Come fight me
in the open, ya coward!
[dinging]
Well, if it isn't
the 'lil weakling.
[KATSURAGI] You again.
Ugh.
[HIKAGE] You're even
weaker than I thought.
[KATSURAGI] Great, just my luck.
I'd choose
someone more exciting
if it weren't for my orders.
[KATSURAGI] To be honest,
I'm glad to fight you again.
Hm.
[KATSURAGI] Gives me
another chance to beat ya
and you'd better believe I'm
gonna take advantage of it!
[Hikage laughing]
[Katsuragi power yell]
[HIKAGE] Ha...
[KATSURAGI] Damn you!
You're a peculiar one.
Huh?
[HIKAGE] Just relax. Why're you
getting so hot and bothered?
Ugh!
Because that's
the only way I know...
[KATSURAGI] ...to win a fight
against the likes of you!
[gasp]
Fights aren't
won with emotion.
[HIKAGE]
They're won with skill.
How the hell'd you do that?
I simply used my ability to
be much better than you are.
[bird chirping]
Where am I?
♪
[HOMURA] Fancy meeting you here.
[gasp] Huh?
[chuckle]
[HOMURA] Thanks again for
helping me out the other day.
Homura, it
really is you. Then--
Do me a favor and try
not to look so scared, okay?
Real shinobi don't get scared.
[ASUKA] But I thought...
we were friends.
The only reason I
befriended you was so I could
find out who you are and what
you're capable of as a shinobi.
[ASUKA] But why?
That's simple.
You're the granddaughter
of the legendary shinobi Hanzo.
[gasp]
Let's see what you got.
Come on, Asuka.
I am Homura, one
of the Hebijo Clandestine
Girl's Academy elite five.
It's been fun
but playtime's over.
I don't get it, how
can you be an evil ninja?
[HOMURA] Aw c'mon,
don't take it personally.
I'm only following orders.
I don't wanna do this.
But I've gotta
take care of business.
♪
[ASUKA] What intense bloodlust!
[Asuka gasp]
[HOMURA] You're really
afraid, aren't you?
[Asuka screaming]
I expected more
from the granddaughter
[HOMURA] of the
legendary shinobi!
I bet he'd be pretty
disappointed in you
right about now.
You don't know my grandpa.
You don't know anything!
You give up?
No, I'm gonna
make my grandpa proud!
Time to die!
[ASUKA] I'm gonna defeat you!
[power yell]
Well, look at that.
You're really givin' it
everything you've got now,
aren't ya?
[HOMURA] Not too shabby.
But I'm still not sure you're
even worth drawing my swords.
[ASUKA] I really
liked you, Homura.
I thought you and I might
even become friends.
But you're untrustworthy.
You've done nothing but
use me ever since we met.
[Asuka] Homura!
Are you really
that naive, Asuka?
I'd take out my
own flesh and blood
if that's what I
was ordered to do!
Don't you get it?
I'm a shinobi!
[ASUKA] Well, so am I!
[Homura grunt]
[Asuke grunt]
No way!
[ASUKA] I did it!
[Homura intense laughing]
Looks like you might be worth
drawing my swords after all.
[gasp]
[HIBARI] What's
this weird feeling?
I've felt it before.
Huh?
Well, hello there.
[HIBARI] You. I know you.
You're just as
adorable as you can be.
Like a frightened
little bunny rabbit
being held against her will.
You were there that day.
[HIBAI] I remember.
Wait, does that mean
you're the puppet master?
[chuckles]
[HARUKA] There's no
reason to be afraid.
Come on over here
little bunny rabbit.
How the heck am I ever
supposed to beat her in a fight?
[HIBARI] I could
use your help Yagyu!
Shinobi Transformation.
[Yagyu gasp]
Hibari must be in
a different kekkai.
[heavy breathing]
You've got some legs on you,
but you're not fast enough
to outrun me, ya hussy!
If I can take her down
then I might be able
to move into another kekkai.
Why're you ignoring me and
acting like you're not afraid?!
Ah! All right, at least
you seem ready to face me
in one-on-one combat now.
But, I'm in a hurry, so
we'll have to make it quick.
You have got some nerve
to make such demands of me!
Ah! Screw this!
[MIRAI] Secret Ninja Art.
Valkyrie, go!
[MIRAI] Ignore me, will ya?
You're gonna pay!
[MAN] Are you telling me
this mission is no longer for
the purpose of stealing their
super secret ninja art scroll?
[SUZUNE] No, this mission is
laying the groundwork for that.
I personally trained the
elite five and helped them
hone their skills as shinobi.
There is no cause for concern.
[MAN] It is said that the
evil ninja's Scroll of Yin,
and the good ninja's Scroll,
the scroll of Yang,
were originally one.
Let me remind you,
it is our destiny
to combine the
scrolls once again.
We've waited a long time
for this and I will not rest
until it is done.
[SUZUNE]
I understand completely.
[SUZUNE] He talks about
"our destiny" but I know
he's concerned with fulfilling
his own selfish desires. Hm!
[SUZUNE] He's such
a vulgar snob.
♪
[ASUKA] Homura,
you're the enemy?
[HOMURA] Are you surprised?
[ASUKA] Yeah!
[HOMURA] Well, here's
a bigger surprise.
I go to the tanning
salon to give my skin
this sexy, golden hue.
[ASUKA] Seriously?
[HOMURA] Sucker.
Next time, "Interlocking
Shinobi Kekkai Barriers".
[ASUKA] Come and get it like
your life depends on it!