[armor cracks]
[laughs]
[KIRIYA] Why did you do it?
Why did you choose
to become an evil ninja?
The answer to
that question...
...is on the paper
you hold in your hand.
A map leading to Hebijo?
What else did you expect?
I'll be awaiting
your arrival, Sensei.
No, wait!
There's no need to hide,
girls, so come on out.
[Asuka gasps]
But how did you
know we were here?
[Katsuragi jumps]
Can't get nothin'
past our sensei.
I thought I ordered you
to stay in your rooms
and wait for me to return.
We're terribly sorry,
sir. It's just that,
you were kinda acting out of
sorts and we were worried.
That's all.
I don't blame you.
[YAGYU]
Kiriya-sensei.
Huh?
Hebijo Academy. You know
where it is, don't you?
I do, thanks to this.
♪
[IKARUGA] That's
where Hebijo Academy is?
[KATSURAGI] It's pretty
far into the mountains, huh?
[KIRIYA] It's in an area
considered to be off-limits
because it's a cultural
heritage conservation site.
They must've had a
powerful company with
evil ninja connections
pull some strings for them.
It may be dangerous
but you've gotta
let us go and
save Hibari!
Yeah! We need to bust
her outta there!
[KIRIYA] I'm afraid
I cannot allow that.
Why not?
But, Sensei!
Because this is a very
delicate situation.
It's far too risky
for good ninja to go
charging into
evil ninja territory.
Ikaruga is absolutely right.
The last thing we want to
do is start an all-out war
of good ninja
against evil ninja.
Shinobi are
supposed to be shadows
that exist within
the larger society.
If those shadows were
to battle each other,
any repercussions could
affect the entire nation.
I just don't get it.
Why do we have
to keep in check?
They're the ones who
came here and attacked us!
[KIRIYA] She's got a point.
I don't understand why
the evil ninja would
violate our tacit agreement.
[KIRIYA] Perhaps it was
just an arbitrary action
taken by Hebijo.
[KIRIYA] Rin.
What is your objective?
Sensei, we can't
just leave Hibari
with them like this!
Hmmm.
[HANZO] Yin and Yang. Such is
the way of the world, ladies.
[ASUKA] Grandpa!
[KIRIYA]
Master Hanzo.
For you see, without
Yin there would be no Yang,
and the opposite
is true as well.
Wait, are you saying that
fighting the evil
ninja is pointless?
[HANZO] No. Their conduct
has been reprehensible.
They act as if
they're above the law.
It's imperative we show
them that's not the case.
The good ninja must
stand up and act as
a shield against their evil.
Forget actin'
like a shield,
let's go and show 'em
who's boss! C'mon--
[YAGYU] Hibari needs me right
now. I'm going to find her.
All by yourself?
Go right ahead.
I won't stop you.
Ultimately, this
is a conflict between
you and your fellow students.
Our fellow students?
[KIRIYA] Hold on. Does that
mean we won't be participating?
[HANZO] Of course not. I
don't see any reason for adults
to get involved
in schoolyard fights.
[KIRIYA] But, sir,
are you sure about this?
I will take
full responsibility.
I promise you, Kiriya.
I won't let anybody
come down on you.
[KIRIYA] Master Hanzo.
[ASUKA] Grandpa?
Alright! We got
the go-ahead!
And no one's gonna
question Master Hanzo!
I don't understand
how you can be so
happy-go-lucky right now.
[snickers]
[HANZO chuckles]
[HANZO] You have no place
calling yourselves shinobi if
you can't even save a friend.
Isn't that right, Yagyu?
Yes, sir.
Very well, if you think
that's best, Master Hanzo,
then I shall give the order.
[IKARUGA] Sensei!
[ASUKA] For real?
I knew you'd come
to your senses!
Well, now that that's settled.
How would you
ladies like a tasty snack?
[GIRLS cheer]
[KATSURAGI] Alright!
Haven't you
forgotten something?
[KATSURAGI] Man, this sucks.
I know he's pissed
'cause we left our rooms
without permission but we've
been out here for hours.
Sensei considers this
part of our training.
Yeah, yeah, I
understand that but--
But what?
It still sucks.
Listen, Katsu.
[IKARUGA] There's no way
of knowing what'll happen.
When we get to Hebijo Academy,
I'm gonna be
counting on you, okay?
Whoa. Who're you and
what've you done with Ikaruga?
Come on, would you please
quit joking around?
Can't you see that I'm
trying to be serious here?
Oh, lighten up! I've been
countin' on you from
the start and I expect
you to do the same with me.
Don't worry. I've got
your back, Chairman.
Ditto.
See? Everything'll
be okay.
Just watch! I know
we can rescue Hibari.
I have no doubt that we'll
save her. I'm so thankful.
Not only does she
have me, but she's got
the three of you looking
out for her as well.
Yep, you know it!
Those evil ninja won't
stand a chance against
us if we all work together!
Yeah.
[Hibari grunts]
[HIBARI] I had a
feeling security might be
pretty lax inside the
castle and I was right.
[HIBARI] I'm sensing a powerful
presence on the top floor.
I bet that's where
they're keeping the
super-secret ninja art scroll.
[MAN] How could
you betray me like this?
[SUZUNE] I'm afraid I don't
understand what you mean.
You gave the
teacher from Hanzo
a map leading right to us.
[MAN] If that isn't a betrayal,
then I don't know what is!
[SUZUNE] Even if we were to
obtain the super-secret
ninja art scroll,
it would be meaningless.
As I've told you before,
it's completely worthless
unless we can bring
about the chosen one.
All I was attempting
to do is facilitate that, sir.
You intentionally called
the Hanzo students here.
So they would be forced in to
a confrontation with my girls.
[SUZUNE] That's correct. The
only way the shinobi students
will reach their
full potential is if they're
pressured to do so.
Bringing them together, and
forcing them to fight, may
be just the impetus they need.
When they tap
into their inner power,
it'll be obvious which
girl is the chosen one.
And if it doesn't work
out that way, then so be it.
I'll just have our girls do
away with the Hanzo shinobi.
[HIBARI gasps]
[MAN] Have you gone insane?
This is a secret facility.
If our superiors
ever found out--
Let us not forget
that you're the one, who was
so eager to succeed, you
decided to act on your own.
[MAN] What?
[SUZUNE] You can either
stay here and face the music,
or you can run away like the
coward we both know you are.
But whatever it is,
leave me out of it.
[MAN] You've got some nerve
disrespecting me like that!
Seize the traitor
Suzune at once!
[HIBARI] The others
are coming here?
[KATSURAGI] What's
wrong with us?
We're not even strong
enough to break some bowls?
[ASUKA] Well, they are
made of plastic, Katsu.
[IKARUGA] And who'd want
to clean up that mess?
[KIRIYA] Ikaruga!
Yes, sir!
[KIRIYA] Katsuragi!
[KIRIYA] Asuka!
Yes, sir!
[KIRIYA] Yagyu!
Your orders
are as follows.
Infiltrate Hebijo
Academy to rescue Hibari
and then recover the
super-secret ninja art scroll!
[ALL] Right!
I've saved the most
important mission for last.
I order all of you,
including Hibari,
to come back to
the Academy alive.
[ALL] Right!
Remember, we're counting
on your victory, ladies,
so go out there
and make us proud!
Shinobi Transformation!
[ALL] Yes, sir!
♪
Go!
[alarm sounds]
Move out!
Preparing to launch!
Here goes! Yahoo!
[ASUKA] This seems
kinda dangerous.
Should we be confronting
them when we can't beat them?
[HANZO] Asuka.
[ASUKA] Grandpa!
Whatever you do,
never forget the
meaning of true power.
I don't get it.
[gasps]
Do you mean this?
[HANZO chuckles] I have to
admit that when I heard
you'd won the scroll,
I was so happy
I couldn't help but
do a dance of joy.
[ASUKA] It's my good luck
charm now. Hey, Grandpa?
Hmmm?
Would you hold
on to it for me?
I need to make some room
in here so I have a place
to store the other scroll
once I get my hands on it.
[HANZO] You got it.
Now off ya go.
[ASUKA] Right!
Okay! Asuka taking off!
[ASUKA] I'm not afraid anymore!
I'm gonna go out there
and make my grandpa proud!
We've got this!
[ASUKA] 'Cause we're
Hanzo Academy shinobi!
Be safe. I know that
you can do it, girls.
[DAIDOJI] Sensei. It
seems it's going to be
harder than we thought.
[KIRIYA] Why do you say that?
[HANZO] This is
about Rin, isn't it?
I suspect that she
was acting on her own
when she gave you
Hebijo Academy's location.
And if that's the case,
when word gets out
she's sure to be punished.
Which is precisely why you
plan to follow the girls.
I may be old, Kiriya,
but you can't fool me.
I didn't think it was
that obvious, sir.
It wasn't, but
it didn't take me long
to put all the
pieces together.
Once I heard that Rin was
tangled up in this mess,
I knew the two of you would
end up getting involved.
Then we've got
nothing to hide from you.
Sensei, I hate to give
you yet another reason
to worry about the girls.
What is it now?
[DAIDOJI] I had a suspicion
about the evil ninja
but after observing
them I know it's true.
They're being held
by a forbidden spell.
[Kiriya gasps]
The girls may
be in trouble!
[HARUKA] Today we're
going to take a tour
of the training
grounds. Sound good?
[HIBARI] I wonder if the others
are on their way here yet.
I've gotta make sure Haruka and
the evil ninja don't find out.
What am I gonna do?
[HARUKA] You're so deep
in thought, Hibari.
Huh?
[HIBARI] Wow, your
training grounds are huge.
How come there's nobody here?
[laughs]
What? You really
can't see them?
[HIBARI gasps]
[HIBARI] So, is this where you
practice camouflage techniques?
[HARUKA] Yep, that's right.
This particular field is used
solely for concealment
drills and nothing else.
I think these shinobi
are all first years.
It's only been
about thirty hours
since they started practicing.
What? But how can they
do it for that long?
[HARUKA] What do you
mean "for that long"?
They haven't even made
it to the halfway point yet.
[HIBARI] Hmmm.
[HIBARI] Lemme guess,
water camouflage techniques?
[YAGYU] Hibari.
Here you go. It's your
turn to try it out.
[HIBARI] I dunno if I'm
gonna be able to do this.
Don't doubt yourself.
I have faith in you, Hibari.
[giggles]
[HIBARI] Yagyu.
Is something wrong?
Oh no, I'm fine.
[MALE TEACHER]
Over there! I can see you!
[HIBARI gasps]
[coughs]
[HIBARI] Don't you think
they're being too hard on her?
[HEBIJO GIRL] I'm sorry to...
[HARUKA] Not at all,
if a student fails
they have to be punished.
It's the only way
they're going to learn.
That's why failure isn't
tolerated at Hebijo Academy.
[Hibari sighs]
What's the matter?
Well, she was hurt, and
her friends saw it happen,
but they didn't do
anything to help her out.
[HOMURA] Yeah, so?
Why should they?
If you ask me, it's
more important to stick around
and make sure the
mission's carried out.
After all, it's not
like she's gonna be
of any help to them
now that she's injured.
[HIBARI] But she's their friend!
[Yomi giggles]
And this is why
girls who've been coddled
all their lives, aren't
cut out to be evil ninja.
[MALE TEACHER]
I can see you, too!
[HEBIJO GIRL] I'm sorry
to disappoint you, sir!
[HARUKA] I realize the
training here is strict, but it
motivates us to work
harder and to aim higher.
We know that we'll be
first-rate shinobi one day.
[HARUKA] You'll understand after
the lecture this afternoon.
[HIBARI] I get it now.
They're so focused on
their goal they'll do
whatever it takes to reach it.
Even if it means
ditching their friends.
Are you coming?
[HIBARI] Yeah!
[Hibari gasps]
My, you're such a clumsy
little girl, aren't you?
[gasps]
I'm so sorry, Haruka!
Don't apologize. It
just makes you cuter.
Thank you.
[ASUKA] I won't
need this anymore.
Are you ready
to go now, Asuka?
Sure thing.
[KATSURAGI] So that's Hebijo
Clandestine Girls' Academy, huh?
[YAGYU] Hibari's being held
somewhere inside those walls.
[IKARUGA] Let's wait here
until the sun goes down.
[MIRAI sighs]
There's nothing
better than a hot bath
after a hard day of training!
[HIBARI] I've gotta try
to get the secret scroll back
before the others make it here.
[HIKAGE] What's wrong?
Do we make you nervous?
[gasps]
[HIBARI] So, um, do you mind
if I ask you guys something?
If it has to do with
sprouts, you're in luck,
because I'm an expert!
No. It's not
about sprouts.
Well, then I don't
know if I can help.
I was wondering
if you could tell me
more about
Suzune-sensei, please?
She's a really
good teacher.
She can be awfully
strict sometimes,
but you can tell that she has
faith in us and our abilities.
Unfortunately, she
doesn't share my interest
in sprouts even
though she raised me.
I wouldn't be the
elegant young lady
you see before you if it
wasn't for Suzune-sensei.
[MAN] Seize the
traitor Suzune at once!
[HOMURA] You okay
there, space cadet?
You aren't startin'
to miss your teacher back
at Hanzo Academy, are ya?
[YOMI] You know you're free
to go back to them if you want.
[HIBARI] Um. No, that's not it!
[HARUKA] That's enough, ladies.
Let's stop picking on my
poor, little Hibari, okay?
She's new, so we should be
extra nice to her. Like this.
I, uh. No
Haruka. Please.
You like it. Don't you?
If you ask me, it looks
like you're the one
who's picking on her, Haruka.
[HARUKA] I'm doing
nothing of the sort.
I'm just showing her some love!
Call it what you
will, but I think
your behavior is
rather indecent.
Goodness, your face is
turning bright red, Mirai.
Are you blushing?
No, if I'm red it's
'cause the bath's hot!
Don't start messin'
with me, Yomi!
[giggles]
[laughs]
What a buncha boneheads.
[HIBARI] The more time I spend
with Haruka and the other girls.
The more I realize that deep
down they're not bad people.
[HARUKA] She had
no other choice but to
become an evil ninja after that.
[YOMI] You're so cute...
[MIRAI] I am not!
You're a big, fat liar!
Cut it out! I'm serious!
[HIBARI] I just know they're
keeping the secret scroll
in that room. I have
to get it back somehow.
[HOMURA] You summoned us, sir?
If you don't mind me
asking, what is this about?
[NARRATOR] A Seclusion
drape. It refracts light
in such a way that its user
blends in with the background.
It makes a great gift for
the peeping tom in your life.
[HIBARI] I'll hide here,
until everyone leaves.
[HOMURA] Suzune-sensei
betrayed us?
[YOMI] But how?
I don't understand.
[MAN] She leaked
Hebijo's location
to the Hanzo Academy shinobi.
[MIRAI] For real? But why
would Sensei do such a thing?
[HARUKA] My, my. Could she
be following in my footsteps?
[MAN] She blindsided me.
I knew Suzune had trained
at Hanzo Academy but I never
doubted her loyalty until now.
[MIRAI] Ha, I knew it!
You mean all the rumors
we heard about her were true?
Our sensei...
[thinks] was a good ninja.
[MAN] Now that the Hanzo
shinobi know where to find us.
It won't be long before
they launch a surprise attack.
When they arrive,
I want you to
intercept them
and wipe them out!
Do I make myself clear?
[ALL] Yes, sir!
It's imperative that
you win this battle, ladies.
Not just for the academy but
for the fate of all evil ninja!
Failure will not be tolerated!
Never!
[sneers]
That's the spirit, Homura.
Such is the earnest
desire of a shinobi.
But I don't want
to take any chances.
Therefore, I will be invoking
the yoke technique immediately.
[NARRATOR] The yoke technique.
An outlawed technique
that gives the caster
control over the
shinobi's life or death.
Basically, if you don't defeat
the enemy it's game over.
As loyal students of
Hebijo Academy, I trust that
none of you will have a
problem with my decision.
If that's not the case,
then please speak up.
It's no big deal.
We knew it would
happen sooner or later.
Yeah. If that's what
you've gotta do.
I'm not worried 'cause I
know we're gonna squash 'em!
They're finished.
The yoke technique
simply adds an element
of excitement to our mission.
Though I doubt
we're in any real danger,
there's nothing
more exhilarating
than putting
your life on the line.
[HIBARI] I have to tell
the others about this!
Oh my, would you
care to tell me
what you're doing
out here, cutie?
[HIBARI] Um. Well, I was
heading back to my room
but I got lost somewhere
along the way.
[HARUKA] Really? Poor thing.
Your sense of
direction's that bad?
I can't believe you
were so lost you wandered
all the way to
the top floor.
[nervous laugh]
[HIBARI] Sorry, I'm
directionally challenged!
Yeah. I'd say so!
You heard everything
that was said, didn't you?
Ah...
[HIBARI] Hey! What do you
think you're doing, Haruka?
I'm sorry about this,
my dear, but we simply
can't afford to have you
interfering with our plans.
[MIRAI] I thought
you were cool.
Silly me, I should've
known the enemy
sent you here to spy on us.
What a naughty girl!
Maybe she'll learn her
lesson if we torture her.
We let our
guard down for you.
[HOMURA] Turns out,
you're nothin' but a traitor.
Homura. Please.
[PATROL NINJA] Let's go!
[hysteria]
[PATROL NINJA 1]
What happened?
[PATROL NINJA 2]
They're over here! Hurry!
[KATSURAGI] This
is gonna be tough.
How're we supposed to get inside
when we can't find the entrance?
Well, if we
can't find it
then hopefully
the others will.
[PATROL NINJA 3] Intruders!
[YAGYU] It looks as though
this bridge will take us
to the rear of the castle.
Yeah, you're right.
[gasps]
Now you be sure
to behave yourself
in there while I'm gone, okay?
Is it true, Haruka?
Are you gonna die if you lose?
Yes, dear,
I'm afraid so.
[HIBARI] But I don't understand
why! It's messed up!
[HARUKA] The headmaster
of Hebijo Clandestine
Girl's Academy has every
shinobi student that
enters the school placed
under the yoke technique.
You can't be serious!
As a heart attack.
Originally, the technique was
only invoked whenever a student
dropped out or attempted
to tell outsiders about
the existence of the school.
[HARUKA] Our headmaster
recently decided to change
the conditions and
it's his right to do so.
But doesn't it scare
you to know that
such a terrible
technique was cast on you?
[Haruka laughs]
"The shinobi who fears
death is the shinobi
who doesn't fear
failing their mission".
Sound familiar,
Suzune-sensei?
Suzune?
[Ikaruga yells]
[Katsuragi yells]
[Aauka yells]
[PATROL NINJA]
We've got intruders, sir!
They appear to be students
from Hanzo Academy!
Damn. They're here
sooner than I thought.
[MAN] Building this academy
was not only time consuming,
it was expensive as well.
If my superiors
get word of this,
I won't just lose my
position, I'll lose my life.
I have been left with
no choice but to use the power
of the super-secret ninja
art scrolls, both Yin and Yang,
to put the organization itself
in the palm of my hands.
[IKARUGA] We've
looked everywhere
and there's still no
sign of the entrance.
I wonder if Asuka and Yagyu
were able to find it.
[ASUKA] Ikaruga! Katsu!
[KATSURAGI] Well,
well, speak of the devil!
[YAGYU] We circled
the entire castle
and we never saw an entrance.
[IKARUGA] In that
case, there must be
a hidden passageway somewhere.
[ASUKA] We've gotta
hurry and find it 'cause
the evil ninja
already know we're here!
[KATSURAGI] Ya don't say!
Thanks for that,
Captain Obvious.
[YAGYU] Hibari.
What's up, Yagyu? Is
there something wrong?
[IKARUGA] Wanna tell
us what you're doing?
[YAGYU] It's Hibari.
I'm picking up her scent.
[KATSURAGI] Seriously?
[ASUKA] You don't think
that could be it, do you?
[IKARUGA] Sure enough.
A hidden passageway.
[KATSURAGI] Alright!
Way to go, Yagyu!
It wasn't me.
It was Hibari.
♪
[YOMI giggles]
[YOMI] We've
been expecting you.
[IKARUGA] Not you again!
[YOMI] Aw, what's the matter?
Aren't you happy to see me?
I'd like to welcome
you ladies to Hebijo Academy.
Now, I hope you've
got what it takes
to at least make
this entertaining.
[HANZO] Asuka, would
you mind storing this
in your top for me?
[ASUKA] No prob, Grandpa!
[HANZO] And this, too.
[ASUKA] Huh?
[HANZO] Oh, and this.
[ASUKA] Okay, but I
can't fit anything else
or my shirt's gonna pop open!
[HANZO] I don't think
you'd hear any complaints
from this audience.
Next time, "Castle Showdown".
[ASUKA] Come and get it
like your life depends on it!