[evil laugh]
[MAN] Yin and Yang.
It's amazing how the scrolls
respond to the fighting
spirit of these girls.
Just a little longer.
It's so close I can taste it.
[laughs]
What's this?
[steel hits steel]
[HOMURA] You'd better say your
prayers, granddaughter of Hanzo!
[HOMURA gasps]
[YOUNG HOMURA]
You took advantage of me.
Why, Komichi-sensei?
How could you?
[KOMICHI] I was ordered
to find and eliminate
the good ninja's successor.
Don't take it personally;
I'm just completing my mission.
[snickers]
[gasps] So, it was all a lie.
The way you treated me.
I thought you actually cared,
but you were just trying
to get close me?
[KOMICHI] What can I say?
It made my job a lot easier.
I can't believe you
lied to gain my trust!
You know my secrets! I even
told you I'm a shinobi student!
Betrayal works best if you gain
the other person's
trust first, Homura.
[gasps]
[KOMICHI] But you know,
it works even better if
you can get them to
feel affection for you.
[glass breaks]
[stab]
You've always had your
grandfather watching over you
so you don't know how
it feels to be betrayed
by someone you love!
I'd choose death
over that any day!
[HOMURA growls]
[ASUKA] I didn't
want to do this.
[screams]
It looks like somebody
finally figured out
how to shift to Yin Style.
You've gotten a lot stronger
since the last time we fought.
[surprised gasp]
Damn! She's got nerve!
[KATSURAGI] I'm lost!
This place is so big I feel like
I'm running around in circles!
Ikaruga.
You shouldn't
scare me like that!
[IKARUGA] Apparently,
there are some hidden stairs
up ahead of us.
Whoa, it's a freakin' map
of the whole castle!
How did you get
your hands on this?
Someone shot
an arrow at me earlier
and the map was attached to it.
[KATSURAGI] Bet it's the
same person who released
the stairs for me and Yagyu!
Who do ya think it could be?
It must be her.
[SUZUNE] Yes.
It's only a matter
of time before the girls
and the scrolls
finally come together.
[KIRIYA] I don't suppose
you'd care to tell me
what you're planning?
[SUZUNE] What brings you here?
Worried about your students?
[KIRIYA] No. At least, not all
of my students. Just one.
[SUZUNE] I simply want
to prove a point, Sensei.
[SUZUNE] After I failed
my mission, I realized that
I could never attain
true power as a good ninja,
because it can
only be found in evil.
I knew that in order
to prove that to you,
I'd have to prevail against
your current shinobi students.
[KIRIYA] In other words, your
half-hearted attacks on Hanzo
were meant to strengthen my
girls so you could defeat them
to prove your point?
[SUZUNE] I knew the fear
of an impending attack would
push you to train them harder.
And look how far they've
come in such a short time.
Very impressive, Kiriya-Sensei.
When the students chosen by
the super-secret
ninja art scrolls fought,
and my student came out on top,
I thought I was well on my way
to achieving my lifelong goal
of becoming a super ninja.
That is, until the
Yin scroll made its way here.
[KIRIYA] Hold on.
You didn't order them
to take the scroll?
[SUZUNE] No, the order
was given by Hebijo's owner
and headmaster, Dogen.
He went behind my back and
contacted the girls directly.
[KIRIYA] What the
hell was he thinking?
Doesn't he know uniting
the Yin and Yang scrolls
is strictly forbidden?
[SUZUNE] This didn't play
out the way I would've liked,
but I must say I'm relieved that
it will all be settled soon.
One of your students
will succeed to the Yin scroll,
and one of mine to the Yang.
Once that happens, the two
girls will be forced to fight.
[KIRIYA] No, we have
to put a stop to this!
[steel clangs]
[SUZUNE] Let the kids
have their fun, Sensei.
This isn't our fight,
it's theirs.
I think it's best we just stand
back and watch what unfolds.
[KIRIYA gasps]
[SUZUNE] Daidoji!
[DAIDOJI] It's been
a long time, Rin.
I think it's a shame that
our reunion was brought about
by such unfortunate
circumstances.
[SUZUNE] It's good to see you
again, my dear underclassman.
Are you still waiting
to defeat me to graduate?
[DAIDOJI] Not anymore.
I've waited long enough.
I've decided that I will
graduate when my underclassmen
crush your students!
[IKARUGA] Are you sure this
is the way to the top floor?
[KATSURAGI] Yeah!
[YOMI giggles]
There's no
getting away from us.
[HIKAGE] You can run--
--but you can't hide, Blondie.
I'm only avoiding
you 'cause I know
you'll die if you lose!
You should thank me
for not kickin' your ass!
What does it matter
to you whether I live or die?
Besides, you can't beat me so
it's not like I'm in danger.
[KATSURAGI]
It just pisses me off.
Can't you see that
asshole's got your lives
in the palm of his hand?
I guess you're not
one to follow orders, huh?
Listen, there's a big difference
between followin' orders,
and handin' your life over
to somebody else!
[KATSURAGI] Now get outta my
way, 'cause I'm comin' through.
There's that
look in your eyes again.
Whenever you stare
at me like that,
this weird sensation
washes over me.
I don't know how
to describe it.
Could it be emotion?
No way.
I learned you can't be a warrior
if you wear your emotions
on your sleeve.
But you do and then it
brings it out in me!
It makes me so
angry! [grunts]
'Bout damn time
you felt somethin'!
I don't understand
why you piss me off so much!
Go ahead.
You may not wanna hear this but
I like you much better this way.
For once, I can
tell you're human.
[chuckles]
You know what to do.
Yeah!
We're pullin' a
"Kiriya-sensei"!
[YOMI coughs]
[YOMI] That's the
oldest trick in the book.
[HIKAGE] We know they're
headed to the top level.
We'll have to cut 'em off
before they get there.
[YOMI] Yeah.
[IKARUGA] If my family
cared half as much,
I wouldn't have
suffered like I did.
[HIKAGE] Yomi. Is
there something wrong?
Oh, no. I'm fine,
but I am worried about you.
Why?
Well, I've never seen
you have an emotional outburst
like that before.
I didn't know
you had a temper.
Neither did I.
[whip]
[HIBARI whimpers]
[HARUKA] Don't tell me
you're giving up already?
[HARUKA] If you're not
gonna put up a fight,
you could at least
scream a little.
Otherwise, this is no fun.
[whip]
[whimper, scream]
[chuckle]
[gasp]
[machine sounds]
[gasps] What the--?
[YAGYU] Touch her again--
--and you'll regret it.
You came to rescue me!
[HARUKA giggles]
I had a feeling
that you'd show up.
[YAGYU] Stop tormenting Hibari!
Aw, do you need
some attention?
Well, I wouldn't mind having
a little fun with you, too!
[crash]
[MIRAI] Thought you
could get away from me, huh?
Don't shoot!
[HARUKA] Ugh, you've got
the worst timing, Mirai.
You always barge in just as
things are getting interesting.
Don't get your
panties in a bunch!
The rest of us deserve to have
a little fun, too, y'know!
This is no time for you
two to be bickering!
So stop!
[MIRAI shouts]
[YAGYU yells]
[HARUKA grunts]
[YAGYU] You wanna try?
[HIBARI] Let's do it!
[BOTH] Secret ninja art!
Come to me, Mr. Bunny!
Hope this works!
[HARUKA gasps]
[MIRAI gasps]
[crashes]
[HARUKA] They performed
a joint secret ninja art.
[MIRAI] I didn't even
know that was possible.
[HARUKA] Ninjutsu is
a skill of the mind.
One of the most
important things I learned
from Suzune-sensei.
And it's true.
What we witnessed
is undeniable proof.
Shinobi can do anything
they put their mind to,
even the impossible.
I envy their friendship.
Me too.
C'mon! Let's
go after them, Mirai!
[thunder]
[gasps]
But I thought I ditched
you! I mean, how did--?
[HOMURA] There's more than one
way to get to the top level!
And I know every nook
and cranny of this place!
Secret ninja art: First Strike!
[ASUKA] Secret ninja art:
Double Sword Slice!
[DOGEN laughs]
Yes, that's it!
Fight until only one
of you is left standing!
I wonder which
one will prevail.
[chuckles]
[ASUKA] Why are we
doing this, Homura?
There's no point in us
fighting each other!
[DOGEN] Congratulations, ladies.
You are the chosen ones!
[ASUKA] Who's he?
[HOMURA] That you,
Master Dogen?
What's this
"chosen one" crap?
Dogen?
Could he be the headmaster
Hibari mentioned?
Listen, Homura.
It is imperative that you
and the Hanzo girl come
to my office immediately.
You will be released
to the guidance
of your respective super-secret
ninja art scrolls.
Me and Asuka?
Master Dogen, what in
the hell's goin' on?
You two are
the chosen ones;
the divine representatives
of the scrolls.
And as such, you have the
ability to obtain the power
of both Yin and Yang.
Therefore, I am commanding
you to deliver that power
directly into my hands.
What? Are you kiddin' me?
There's no way the
organization would allow--
[grunts]
[DOGEN] I gave you
an order, Homura.
Hebijo Clandestine Girls'
Academy and its students
are nothing to me;
they're merely a means
to achieving my dream.
Once I've
attained the power
of the Yin and Yang
scrolls, the evil ninja,
and all other shinobi, will be
forced to bow down before me!
You seriously want me
to betray the organization?
[KATSURAGI] Asuka!
[HIBARI] Are you all right?
Hey, you guys!
What'd you do to her?
What is the meaning
of this, Master Dogen?
That bastard was just
using us to get his hands
on the power of the scrolls.
He tried to get me to
betray the organization.
[MIRAI] What?
[chuckles] Y'know.
Can't say I'm surprised he
turned out to be a traitor.
Am I the only
one who's confused here?
[HIKAGE] Don't
sweat the details.
All you really need to know
is Dogen's our target.
Yeah?
Then you'd better start
sayin' your prayers, pops!
If that's how it's gonna be.
[deep pulse]
[IKARUGA] A shinobi kekkai?
[HIBARI] They're gone!
But where did they go?
[YOMI] Don't tell me.
Dogen must've pulled
them into the kekkai!
[ASUKA] Where are we?
[HOMURA] We're inside
a shinobi kekkai.
If you'd followed my
orders I wouldn't have to go
to such extremes.
Now I've no choice.
Here's my secret
ninja art. Giant Serpent!
[SERPENT roars]
Holy crap! What the
hell are these things?
They're robots,
mechanical shinobi.
Dogen has an entire
army protecting him.
Mechanical?
Don't get the wrong idea;
I wasn't saving you.
I simply saw an opportunity to
strike one down so I took it!
I can't blame you for
being wary but don't forget
we're on the same team now!
I know.
But I'm still
keeping an eye on you.
That was a nice move!
You're right, it was.
Ugh, well so much for humility!
[HARUKA] Uh-oh,
they're surrounded.
[HIBARI] Oh, no!
What're you doin'?
It's important for you
conserve your strength now.
There's a job coming up
that only you can pull off.
[HOMURA] Damn it!
[DOGEN] Try as you might,
there's no defeating
my Giant Serpent.
You're a traitor!
You betrayed me.
Just like he did!
[DOGEN] And you have no
one to blame but yourself!
Perhaps if you
weren't so foolish,
you'd know better than to fall
for the same trick twice.
[HOMURA laughs maniacally]
[ASUKA] Homura?
[HOMURA] Seems you don't know,
who you're messin' with.
The last man who betrayed me,
didn't live to talk about it.
Did you honestly
think you were
gonna get away with this?
I've already committed
the ultimate sin once,
and I'll do it again!
[HOMURA screams]
[DOGEN grunts]
[HOMURA] You're a dead man!
If I'm goin' to hell,
then I'm takin' you with me!
[HOMURA] Lemme go!
[ASUKA] Don't throw
your life away just to get
revenge on that jerk!
[HOMURA] I threw my
life away when I joined
the evil ninja organization,
so why should I start caring
about it now?
Because your friends
would be lost without you!
How do you know?
Friends care
about one another!
That's what they do!
[glass breaks]
[IKARUGA] That was
the last of them.
[KATSURAGI] Now what?
[HARUKA] Dogen must've used the
Yin and Yang super-secret ninja
art scrolls to create that
shinobi kekkai barrier.
It's infinitely more
powerful than the interlocking
kekkai barrier I created.
However, it may be possible
for us to push our way in,
if we work together.
As far as I know,
you're the only shinobi who's
ever been able to successfully
bust into one of 'em.
Yeah, that's true,
but it had very
little to do with me.
It wasn't my power
that got me in.
It was yours, Hibari.
[HIBARI gasps]
What did I tell you?
You're the only one who's
capable of getting us inside.
[HIBARI] Who, me? But how?
By using your
telepathic abilities
to reach out to
Asuka and Homura.
Now you understand
why I told you to
conserve your
strength, right?
I guess it's worth a try.
[HARUKA] Shinobi Kekkai!
[IKARUGA] What're you doing?
[HARUKA] Creating
another barrier in such
close proximity--
--will weaken
the one that they're in.
You ready?
Uh-huh!
I never thought I'd see
the day that good and evil ninja
would be fighting
on the same side.
Me neither.
Are you okay
with us callin' a truce?
Yeah, you bet.
Now let's go rescue them!
We're calling to you.
Can you guys hear us?
We're here for you!
Please listen!
Asuka.
We wanna help but we're
stuck outside the kekkai!
You've gotta call to us!
Dammit!
Are you all right?
What now? [screams]
Know what really
pisses me off?
Not that I might die, it's
that if I do--I won't have
the chance to see
the others again.
--[HIBARI] Asuka!
--[MIRAI] Homura!
What's that?
--[KATSURAGI] Asuka!
--[HARUKA] Homura!
[ASUKA] Our friends
are calling to us.
I know you're fighting,
so it might be tough,
but you've gotta try
to feel our presence.
It's the only way
we can get to you!
[HOMURA] Feel their presence?
What's that mean?
I think they want us
to call out to them
so they can break
into the kekkai!
Then let's get on it!
You're just lowly
shinobi students!
[GIRLS power up]
[DOGEN] What the--?
We did it!
[ASUKA] Thanks, you guys.
I knew you'd come to help.
[HOMURA] Incredible.
I can feel their emotion.
Their rage, and their love.
My friends are
determined to protect me,
and with their support,
I have all the strength I need.
The katana and the shield. It
finally makes sense, Grandpa.
No! Not the scrolls!
[screams]
Prepare to die!
Secret ninja art: Crimson!
Secret ninja art:
Hanzo Style Wild Bloom!
[BOTH scream]
Super-secret ninja arts?
Impossible!
[DOGEN screams]
Thanks, guys.
[DOGEN] You little
brats foiled my plans.
How dare you?
Dogen's trying to escape!
No! We can't
let him get away!
Let's go after him!
[SUZUNE] The Hebijo and Hanzo
students have joined forces?
[KIRIYA] That's what happens
when shinobi are faced
with a common enemy.
[SUZUNE] Wait,
what are you implying?
That everything
I've done was in vain?
But I've never been more
sure of anything before!
Rin, both good and evil
ninja can attain true power.
Our students' strength
doesn't come from affiliation,
nor does it come
from our instruction.
It's because they've
learned the value of friendship.
A lesson that is essential
for any shinobi looking
to attain true power.
The bonds of
friendship are stronger
than anything.
We all need someone
to help with the hard times.
And the girls have all
found that in each other.
♪
[DOGEN] Suzune? And
the teacher from Hanzo?
How about you leave
these young ladies alone
and pick on
somebody your own size?
Somebody like me!
No. Don't you
come any closer to me!
Damn! I've got no choice!
[SUZUNE] You activated
the self-destruct device?
If I'm going down,
then so are you!
[SUZUNE] Are you insane, Dogen?
What about the hundreds of
students who're still inside
the castle?
You don't honestly
think I care, do you?
'Cause I don't. I won't lose
any sleep if they die.
[laughs]
[STUDENTS scream]
We have to go
save the other students!
With so many
girls still inside,
you'll need our help!
[HIKAGE] I don't think
that's a good idea.
[HARUKA] The castle's huge and
extremely difficult to navigate.
[MIRAI] Yeah, to be honest,
you'd probably
just slow us down.
[YOMI] Hurry and get
to safety while you can.
But, you guys!
Don't worry. I'll be
back to kick your ass.
We have no choice but
to take them at their word.
[DOGEN chuckles]
Either way,
students are going to die.
It's impossible for the elite
five to rescue everyone.
But if you refuse to release me,
I'll invoke the yoke technique
and none of them will
make it out alive.
[DAIDOJI] I knew you were up to
no good, you heartless bastard!
You allowed him
to use a forbidden technique
on your students?
He convinced me
it was a good idea because
it would keep Hebijo's
secrets from being exposed.
This castle's going
to crumble any minute now.
You should release me
before that happens.
[IKARUGA] You're
not going anywhere!
What the hell?
Let me go!
[SUZUNE] True power has
nothing to do with whether
a ninja is good or evil.
And that is the lesson
my students taught
their teacher today.
Some sensei
I turned out to be.
What do
you think you're doing?
You're going to fall!
Goodbye, Sensei.
Please don't ever forget me.
[KIRIYA gasps]
[DOGEN grunts]
[DAIDOJI] No!
[GIRLS gasps]
[KIRIYA] Rin!
[ALL] Welcome back!
[IKARUGA] Welcome back!
Everything go okay?
Yep, I'm happy
to say that I passed
my advancement test!
Congratulations, Asuka.
I knew you could do it!
[KATSURAGI] Good goin',
Boobalicious!
[ASUKA] Cut it out!
I swear, I'm never sharing
good news with you again!
[HIBARI] It took you a while,
but you've finally made it
to the same level as Yagyu!
[ASUKA] What? Aw, man.
Thanks a lot.
You just had to go and
remind me, didn't you?
[GIRLS cough]
[KIRIYA] So I hear
you passed your test.
[ASUKA] Yeah! I did my best!
About time you reached
the same rank as Yagyu,
your underclassman.
[whimpers] Geez! Sorry
I'm such a late bloomer.
[KIRIYA] Nonsense.
You've made me, and your
grandfather, very proud.
I'm glad you're home.
Now we can start training again.
Hope you ladies are ready to get
back into the swing of things.
[ALL] Yes, sir!
But first,
I should tell you.
Headquarters sent me
a report on the Hebijo
Academy investigation.
[KIRIYA] Officials searched
through the castle's ashes with
a fine-toothed comb, but there
was no sign of the elite five.
[IKARUGA] Do you
think that means
they got out of there safely?
[YAGYU] There's no
way of knowing but
I choose to believe they did.
[HIBARI] Yeah, you
know what? Me, too!
[KATSURAGI] They're
tough as nails.
They'll be back to pick
a fight with us someday.
[ASUKA] Somehow, I just know
that we'll see them again.