- ( theme song playing )
- ( singing in Japanese )
- ( pitter-patter or rain )
- THIS IS RIDICULOUS.
HOW LONG IS IT GONNA TAKE?
- WE'RE NOT JUST TALKING ABOUT
SCRAPES AND BRUISES, SEIJI.
IT'S A BIT MORE COMPLICATED.
TWO OR THREE OF HIS RIBS
HAVE BEEN SHATTERED.
HE HAS ABDOMINAL LACERATIONS,
AND HIS LUNG HAS A HOLE
THE SIZE OF A FIST.
- I CAN'T BELIEVE
THAT LITTLE BEAST
OF A CHILD DID THIS TO HIM.
KOUHEI WAS THERE TO SAVE HER.
HE WAS POWERLESS, BUT HE TRIED
ANYWAY. AND SHE BETRAYED HIM!
- SEIJI, WHAT HAPPENED
IN THAT BUILDING
CANNOT BE BLAMED ON HER.
- WHAT DOES THAT MEAN?
SHE WAS THE ONE
WHO INFLICTED THE WOUNDS!
- COUNT KINKEL HAD
CONTROL OF HER MIND,
SHE WAS NOTHING
BUT A PUPPET.
ANY ANGER YOU HAVE SHOULD
BE SAVED FOR HIM.
AND THERE'S NO TELLING
WHERE HE IS NOW.
I CAN'T SENSE ANYTHING FROM THE
SHIKIGAMI I SENT AFTER HIM.
WE CAN ONLY HOPE HE
DOESN'T COME FOR MORE.
- HE WON'T MAKE HIS MOVE
IN THE DAYLIGHT.
NOT A BLOODSUCKING
CREATURE LIKE HIM!
- BLINDED BY FURY. I WAS RIGHT
TO SEND THE CHILD HOME.
- I'M SO CONFUSED.
WHAT HAPPENED
IN THAT ROOM?
- ( thunder rumbles )
- KOUHEI WAS STANDING
IN FRONT OF ME.
I JUST KNEW HE WAS,
LIKE YOU DO IN A DREAM.
BUT THEN...
BIG BROTHER, PLEASE!
WHAT HAPPENED? HOW DID
KOUHEI GET HURT?
IT'S NO USE.
I CAN'T REMEMBER IT AT ALL.
- ( clock ticking )
- I DON'T KNOW WHAT ELSE TO DO.
I TRIED EVERYTHING.
- WELL, WHAT EXACTLY IS
KOUHEI SUPPOSED TO BE TO YOU?
- HE'S SUPPOSED TO BE MY SLAVE.
- ( he laughs )
- THAT'S THE LIFE FOR YOU, BOY!
GO ON, NOW!
BE THIS YOUNG GIRL'S SLAVE!
- GIVE IT A REST.
- WELL, HE'S GOT A POINT!
YOU CAN'T GO. YOU HAVE TO
STAY WITH YOUR MASTER.
HEY! HAVEN'T YOU PUT
THE SEAWEED IN YET?
- UH-UH. FIGURED I'D
ADD IT IN LATER.
- IT'S MISO SOUP. YOU HAVE TO
COOK THE INGREDIENTS!
- JUST LET ME DO IT!
- HEY!
IT'S MY STUFF! GO AWAY!
WELL, I'M THE ONE
WHO BROUGHT IT OVER HERE,
- JUST LET ME SEE WHAT IT IS!
- IT'S UNDERWEAR, OKAY?
- UNDER... DON'T SHOW ME THAT!
- I WASN'T GOING TO,
YOU NOSY IDIOT!
- YOU THINK I'M JUST GONNA SIT
THERE WHILE YOU SUCK MY BLOOD?
- YOU'RE MY SLAVE, DUMMY!
THAT'S YOUR JOB!
- QUIT CALLING ME YOUR SLAVE!
I'M NOT YOUR SLAVE!
YOU JUST KEEP THINKING
THAT I AM!
- YOU NEVER LISTEN
TO ME, KOUHEI.
YOU'RE A BIG, STUBBORN JERK
WHO MAKES A BIG DEAL OUT
OF THE STUPIDEST THINGS!
BUT STILL,
YOU'RE MY FIRST SLAVE.
- Luna: AND NOW
YOU'RE ALL ALONE AGAIN.
BUT THAT CAN'T BE HELPED.
IT HAPPENS EVERY TIME.
LONELINESS IS SOMETHING
YOU SHOULD LEARN TO ACCEPT.
LONELINESS IS YOUR DESTINY.
- NO! WHAT IS THAT DOING HERE?
I THREW IT AWAY AT THE CASTLE!
- Luna: BUT YOU
CAN'T BE SURPRISED.
IT'S ALWAYS BEEN YOUR FATE
TO BE ALONE.
ANY HUMAN WHO GETS CLOSE TO
YOU WILL BE CURSED,
AND INEVITABLY DIE
BECAUSE OF WHAT YOU ARE.
YOU DRINK HUMAN BLOOD.
YOU DESTROY THEIR LIVES.
BUT THAT'S OKAY.
BECAUSE YOU ARE A BLUE BLOOD,
A VAMPIRE OF NOBLE LINEAGE
AND IT IS YOUR RIGHT.
- NO! SHUT UP! I HATE YOU!
I DON'T HAVE TO LISTEN
TO YOUR LIES ANYMORE!
- ( door opens )
- MASTER? WHAT'S WRONG?
- LIKE, TAKE THIS PRESENT
FOR EXAMPLE.
HE WENT OUT AND BOUGHT
IT FOR YOU,
PUT IT IN A NICE GIFT
BAG AND EVERYTHING.
BUT FOR SOME REASON HE TOLD ME
TO GIVE IT YOU INSTEAD,
LIKE IT WAS MY IDEA.
- KOUHEI.
I HAVE TO SEE HIM.
- ( pitter-patter of rain )
- COME ON! YOU DIDN'T FORGET
ANYTHING, DID YOU?
- UH-UH.
- HEY, GIRLS. HOW ARE YOU?
- JUST OUR LUCK.
THE ONE PERSON IN THE WORLD
WE DIDN'T WANNA SEE.
- WHAT ARE YOU DOING HERE?
I THOUGHT YOU WERE IN KYOTO?
- GRANDFATHER RYUUHEI
ASKED US TO COME.
WE DIDN'T GET MANY DETAILS
OVER THE PHONE,
HE JUST SAID KOUHEI WAS HURT.
AS LONG AS YOU'RE HERE,
WHY DON'T YOU DO SOMETHING
USEFUL AND FILL US IN.
- WHAT?
- TELL US ABOUT KOUHEI!
WHY'S HE IN THE HOSPITAL?
YOU MEAN YOU
LIVE WITH HIM
AND YOU DON'T EVEN
KNOW WHAT HAPPENED?
- NO. SORRY.
- WHAT ARE YOU SAD ABOUT?
DID YOU LOSE A FANG?
WAIT, WHAT ARE YOU SAYING?
YOU THINK SHE'S WORRIED
ABOUT KOUHEI TOO?
- NO, I'M NOT! I DON'T CARE
WHAT HAPPENS TO THAT JERK!
I JUST... I HATE LOOKING FOR
NEW SLAVES, THAT'S ALL.
- DON'T WORRY, MASTER!
IT'LL BE A-OK!
- YOU! YOU'RE THAT
SHIKIGAMI THEY SAVED!
- DON'T BOTHER PROTECTING
YOURSELF, MASTER.
KOUHEI'S GONNA BE FINE.
HE'S TOO STUBBORN TO KEEL OVER
FROM AN ITTY-BITTY
INJURY LIKE THIS!
I CAN GUARANTEE YOU
HIS SURVIVAL!
- THOSE ARE PRETTY UPPITY WORDS,
COMING FROM A TALKING CAT.
- I'LL BE HAPPY
IF YOU'RE RIGHT, THOUGH.
- WELL, YOU'RE ALREADY
HERE, SUCK-FACE.
YOU MIGHT AS WELL COME ALONG.
- YES, WE'RE FAMILY.
THANK YOU.
THE SURGERY'S OVER.
HE'S IN RECOVERY, ON
THE 5TH FLOOR! LET'S GO!
- I'M COMING, KOUHEI.
- BIG BROTHER!
- THE OPERATION WENT WELL.
BUT WE STILL NEED YOUR HELP.
- KOUHEI!
IT'S ALL AROUND HIM.
THE SHADOW OF DEATH.
- THE HOSPITAL STAFF
HAS DONE EVERYTHING
WE COULD'VE
EXPECTED FROM THEM.
BUT IT WON'T BE ENOUGH.
DOCTORS ALONE CAN'T
CURE THIS WOUND.
OUR PERFORMANCE TONIGHT
WILL BE CRITICAL.
ALL THAT YOU'VE
LEARNED WILL BE TESTED
UNDER THE HIGHEST OF STAKES.
- ARE YOU TWO PREPARED?
- YES.
- LET GO!
- LEAVE IT TO US, CHILD.
I KNOW YOU'RE UPSET,
BUT THERE'S NOTHING YOU
CAN DO FOR HIM NOW.
- NO, I WANT TO BE
WITH HIM, TOO! HE'S MY SLAVE!
- NOW IS NOT THE TIME
TO BE STUBBORN!
- BUT I SAW IT! THE SHADOW
OF DEATH! IT'S CLAIMING HIM!
IF WE DON'T HELP HIM SOON
IT'LL BE TOO LATE!
- ( slap )
- THIS IS YOUR FAULT.
HE'S HERE BECAUSE OF YOU.
AND NOW YOU HAVE THE
NERVE TO INTERFERE
WHEN WE'RE TRYING TO SAVE HIM.
HOW DEEP DOES YOUR
BLOOD LUST GO?
- SEIJI! YOU'RE OUT OF LINE.
BLAME FALLS ON THE COUNT.
- SO YOU SAY.
- YOUR DISSENT HAS BEEN NOTED.
BUT NOW IS NOT THE
TIME TO BRING THIS UP!
- I WON'T SAY MORE BECAUSE
I DON'T KNOW WHAT HAPPENED.
BUT WE HUMANS WILL HANDLE
IT FROM HERE.
YOU'D ONLY CAUSE MORE TROUBLE.
- I'M SORRY, CHILD.
PRAY FOR HIS HEALTH.
IT'S THE ONLY THING YOU CAN DO.
- ( heart monitor beeping )
- HIS BODY IS STABLE FOR NOW,
BUT THESE ARE NOT
NORMAL INJURIES.
THE SPIRITS HAVE ALREADY
STAKED THEIR CLAIM ON HIM.
WE MUST SYNERGIZE OUR KI,
AND CAST AWAY THE SHADOW
OF DEATH. UNDERSTOOD?
- WE'RE READY.
- SEIJI, YOU MAY BEGIN.
- LOOMING APPARITION THAT
KNOWS NOT OF HEAVEN'S CALL.
HEAR MY COMMAND.
RETURN TO THE DARKNESS
FROM WHICH YOU CAME.
REPAY OUR PATIENCE.
RELEASE THIS SOUL.
BACK NOW TO THE
EDGE OF IMMORTALITY.
THIS IS YOUR FAULT.
HE'S HERE BECAUSE OF YOU.
- BUT WE HUMANS
WILL HANDLE IT FROM HERE.
YOU'D ONLY CAUSE MORE TROUBLE.
- PRAY FOR HIS HEALTH.
IT'S THE ONLY THING YOU CAN DO.
- THEY'RE RIGHT. HUMANS HELP.
VAMPIRES DESTROY.
- HEAR MY VOICE. HEED MY WORDS.
PASS THROUGH THE DARKNESS INTO
LIGHT. TO OUR WORLD YOU RETURN.
TRAVEL THE PATH
DOWN WHICH I LEAD.
MOVE TOWARD THE THRESHOLD.
RESTORE YOUR WILL.
FOLLOW THE PORTAL BACK TO LIFE.
LEAVE BEHIND...
- CONCENTRATE, GIRLS.
UNITE YOUR KI.
- THROUGH ME IS THE WAY.
- Luna: IT'S ALWAYS BEEN
YOUR FATE TO BE ALONE.
ANY HUMAN WHO GETS CLOSE TO YOU
WILL BE CURSED,
AND INEVITABLY DIE.
BECAUSE OF WHAT YOU ARE.
YOU DRINK HUMAN BLOOD.
YOU DESTROY THEIR LIVES.
- HEAR MY VOICE. HEED MY WORDS.
PASS THROUGH THE DARKNESS
INTO LIGHT.
TO OUR WORLD YOU RETURN. TRAVEL
THE PATH DOWN WHICH I LEAD.
MOVE TOWARD THE THRESHOLD.
RESTORE YOUR WILL.
FOLLOW THE PORTAL BACK TO LIFE.
LEAVE BEHIND THE SHADOW
OF DEATH. THROUGH ME IS THE WAY.
RELEASE HIM, SPIRITS.
RETURN HIS SOUL.
RELEASE HIM, SPIRITS. RETURN
HIS SOUL. THROUGH ME IS THE WAY.
IT ISN'T WORKING.
DEATH IS ANCHORED DEEP.
- ( bell jingles )
- ( tires screech )
- HAZUKI! THERE YOU ARE!
- YOU'RE MY SLAVE, DUMMY!
- QUIT CALLING ME YOUR SLAVE!
- I CALL UPON THE ELEMENTS.
EARTH, FIRE, WIND, WATER.
BE HERE NOW. LEND US THE
STRENGTH OF YOUR WILLS.
HEAR MY VOICE. HEED MY WORDS.
PASS THROUGH THE DARKNESS
- INTO LIGHT.
- KAORU!
- TO OUR WORLD YOU RETURN...
- THESE RITES HAVE
GONE ON FOR HOURS.
THE BODY CAN'T HANDLE
ANY MORE.
KOUHEI, I'M NOT SURE
WE CAN SAVE YOU.
- ( Kouhei groans )
- BEHIND THE SHADOW OF DEATH...
- ( bell jingles )
- AN OMEN.
- HAZUKI, IT'S OKAY.
I NEED YOU TO LISTEN TO ME NOW.
- MAMA?
- MAYBE IT IS TRUE. MAYBE WE
VAMPIRES ARE A CURSED RACE.
- MAMA, WHERE ARE YOU?
- BUT THERE IS MORE
TO US THAN DESTRUCTION
AND THE DRAINING OF LIFE.
THE POWER OF BLOOD
FLOWS TWO WAYS.
AND THERE IS SOME
GOOD YOU CAN DO.
- MAMA!
SOME GOOD I CAN DO?
WHAT DOES SHE MEAN?
- PASS THROUGH THE DARKNESS
INTO LIGHT.
TO OUR WORLD YOU RETURN. TRAVEL
THE PATH DOWN WHICH I LEAD.
MOVE TOWARD THE THRESHOLD.
RESTORE YOUR WILL.
FOLLOW THE PORTAL BACK TO
LIFE. LEAVE BEHIND...
- ( door opens )
- KOUHEI!
- HAZUKI, GO HOME.
- MOVE!
I'M SORRY.
- WHAT'S THIS?
- YOU'RE MY FIRST SLAVE, AND I
WON'T LET YOU LEAVE ME NOW.
NOT HERE. NOT LIKE THIS.
IF YOU DO,
I'LL NEVER FORGIVE YOU!
- ( heart monitor beeping )
- WHERE'RE YOU GOING, HAZUKI?
- LIKE YOU SAID, IT'S MY FAULT
HE GOT HURT. SO...
- EASY NOW.
YOU KNOW, YOU'VE STILL GOT
A LOT TO LEARN ABOUT PEOPLE.
- BUT I...
- KOUHEI WLL BE DISAPPOINTED
IF YOU ARE NOT HERE
WHEN HE WAKES UP.
- WHAT'S WRONG?
- KOUHEI!
- COME ON!
WHAT ARE YOU CRYING FOR?
- THAT GLOW, WHEN SHE BIT HIM...
- YES. I'VE NEVER SEEN
ANYTHING QUITE LIKE IT.
IT LOOKED LIKE PART OF
HER LIFE ENERGY.
- THAT'S THE CONCLUSION
I CAME TO AS WELL.
THAT MEANS SHE SHORTENED HER
OWN LIFE TO SAVE HIS.
- SEEMS I WAS WRONG ABOUT
THE LITTLE BEAST AFTER ALL.
- BACK ON YOUR FEET, KAORU.
FEELING BETTER NOW?
- AH, COME ON, YOU'RE
EMBARRASSING ME.
- I MISSED YOU, YOU BIG IDIOT!
- YEAH, I... WAIT A SECOND,
DID YOU BITE ME AGAIN?
- SEE? I TOLD YOU IT'D BE A-OK!
- ( she sighs )
- TOO BAD WE COULDN'T
STAY LONGER.
SCHOOL JUST CAN'T COMPETE WITH
ADVENTURES IN THE PARANORMAL.
MAYBE OUR TEACHER'LL
GET POSSESSED.
WELL, AT LEAST KOUHEI'S OKAY.
WOULDN'T MAKE MUCH OF A
FUTURE HUSBAND ON A SLAB.
- UH-HUH.
- YOU OKAY?
- I JUST HOPE HE ISN'T
STILL IN DANGER.
- ARE YOU REALLY OKAY LEAVING
THE HOSPITAL SO SOON?
- DOCTORS CLEARED IT.
SAID THEY'D NEVER SEEN ANYONE
RECOVER FROM SURGERY THIS FAST.
I FEEL BETTER THAN I
HAVE IN YEARS. OUCH!
- YOU'RE SO FULL OF IT! I TOLD
YOU, YOU SHOULD'VE STAYED!
- SORRY, BRAT.
I TRIED TO BE A HERO, BUT I'M
THE ONE WHO NEEDED SAVING.
- NO, KOUHEI. YOU SAVED ME
IN LOTS OF WAYS.
- OH, MAN. FEELS LIKE I HAVEN'T
BEEN HOME FOR MONTHS.
- WELL, I'M GLAD YOU'RE HERE
NOW. AND THAT I'M HERE, TOO.
- HAVING TUBES DOWN YOUR
THROAT REALLY MAKES YOU THIRSTY.
BREW ME SOME TEA,
WILL YA, BRAT?
- BREW SOME... WHO DO YOU
THINK YOU ARE? MY MASTER?
- I'M THINKING I'M
MORE LIKE A GUY
WHO JUST CRAWLED OFF A GURNEY.
- COME ON, DON'T BE
ALL DIFFICULT.
- OH, I'M BEING DIFFICULT?
A SLAVE DOES NOT TELL
HIS MASTER TO BREW TEA!
- SHOW SOME COMPASSION!
- YOU SHOW SOME DECENCY!
- BRAT!
- JERK!
- ( Kinkel laughs )
- YES, THAT'S IT.
THAT'S THE LOOK.
HOW MANY YEARS,
DECADES HAS IT BEEN,
SINCE I'VE SEEN THAT
ON YOUR FACE?
YOU WERE MERELY A
HUMAN SLAVE BACK THEN.
I WOULD BE HARD ON YOU,
PUSH YOU, ABUSE YOU.
THEN LOOSEN THE REINS.
AND THAT'S WHEN YOU'D LOOK AT
ME WITH THOSE IRRESISTIBLE EYES.
I COULD NEVER TELL IF YOU WERE
BEGGING FOR MERCY,
OR BEGGING FOR MORE.
AND WHEN YOU FINALLY SURRENDERED
YOUR HEART TO ME,
I HAD SUCH AN OVERWHELMING
SENSE OF COMPLETION.
- I HATE TO DISAPPOINT
YOU, COUNT,
BUT I'M NOT SO OBEDIENT ANYMORE.
- YES, THAT'S THE BEAUTY OF IT.
THE BLOOD OF THAT BOY IS EVEN
STRONGER THAN I EXPECTED.
HE'S GIVEN YOU THE POWER TO
RESIST ME FOR THIS LONG.
AND GIVEN ME THE CHANCE TO BREAK
YOU, ALL OVER AGAIN.
I WILL HAVE TO THANK HIM
MIGHTILY WHEN HE ARRIVES
RATHER SOON
WITH MISTRESS LUNA.
- ( she gasps )
- SHE WILL FIND HER TRUE HOME.
AND HE WILL FIND HIS GRAVE.
PREPARATIONS FOR THE WELCOMING
PARTY HAVE ALREADY BEEN MADE.
- ( theme song playing )
- ( singing in Japanese )
- WELL, HOW'D YOU LIKE
TODAY'S MOON PHASE?
OF COURSE I THOUGHT IT
WAS THE BEST,
BECAUSE BIG BROTHER
ENDED UP OKAY,
AND HE CAME BACK HOME
WHERE HE BELONGS.
EVEN IF HE CAN BE AN ANNOYING
NITWIT SOMETIMES.
BUT THERE'S A NEW PROBLEM.
KOUHEI DOESN'T FEEL LIKE
DOING ANYTHING NOW
AFTER HIS WHOLE ORDEAL!
AND WE'VE GOTTA FIGURE OUT
SOMETHING QUICK,
BECAUSE THERE'S REAL
TROUBLE ON THE WAY.
NOW THAT THE COUNT
KNOWS THE TRUTH,
HE WON'T STAY AWAY FOR LONG!
NEXT EPISODE: "BIG BROTHER,
GET SOME REST!"
BECAUSE WE KNOW YOU'RE
GONNA NEED IT. SEE YA THEN!