- YOU FEELING OKAY, GRAMPS?
- WE THOUGHT THE DOCTOR CLEARED
YOU TO LEAVE THE HOSPITAL
- I'VE BEEN PUTTING OFF
TELLING YOU TWO,
BUT MY CONDITION IS MUCH MORE
SERIOUS THAN WE THOUGHT.
THE DOCTOR HAS TOLD ME
I'M GOING TO NEED TO
STAY HERE MUCH LONGER.
- I HOPE THIS "CONDITION"
DOESN'T INVOLVE
GIRLS IN WHITE HATS.
- I HAVE NO IDEA WHAT YOU MEAN.
- COME ON, GRAMPS, DID
YOU REALLY HAVE TO MOVE
INTO A PRIVATE VIP SUITE?
THESE ROOMS ARE EXPENSIVE.
HOW ARE YOU SUPPOSED
TO PAY FOR IT?
PLEASE DON'T TELL ME YOU'RE
AUCTIONING THE HOUSE.
- DON'T WORRY, KOUHEI,
I HAD A LOVELY CHAT WITH
THE BILLING DEPARTMENT
AND I CONVINCED THEM TO
GIVE ME A SPECIAL RATE
WITH SOME HELP FROM MY
SECRET HYPNOSIS POTION.
( laughing )
- IT'S A GOOD THING YOU WEREN'T
MORE AMBITIOUS IN LIFE.
- ( theme song playing )
- ( singing in Japanese )
- Kouhei: ANY NEWS ON KINKEL?
- Seiji: NOTHING YET.
- ( sighs )
IF WE COULD JUST FIND ELFRIEDE,
WE'D BE AT LEAST ONE STEP
CLOSER TO FINDING THE COUNT.
- SHE'S THE HELPFUL
VAMPIRE, RIGHT?
- ( chuckling )
- ( knock on door )
- COME IN. THE DOOR'S OPEN.
OH. DIDN'T EXPECT TO SEE YOU.
TOO BAD YOU DIDN'T STOP
BY A LITTLE EARLIER.
YOU JUST MISSED
KOUHEI AND SEIJI.
I'M SURPRISED YOU DIDN'T
SEE THEM ON YOUR WAY UP.
YOU'LL HAVE TO GIVE THEM A CALL
AND TELL THEM YOU'RE ALL RIGHT.
THEY'RE PRETTY WORRIED.
THEY HAVEN'T BEEN ABLE TO
REACH YOU THESE PAST FEW DAYS.
- THAT'S WEIRD. DOOR'S OPEN.
I COULD HAVE SWORN I LOCKED IT.
- YOU CAN'T AFFORD TO MAKE
SUCH CARELESS MISTAKES, KOUHEI.
WE'RE IN ENOUGH DANGER AS IT IS.
- HMPH!
DIDN'T ANYONE EVER TEACH YOU
IT'S RUDE TO BE LATE WHEN
YOU HAVE A GUEST?
- GUEST?
- THAT'S WHAT I SAID!
AND SINCE YOU'VE NO CONCEPT
OF TIME AND MASTER IS SLEEPING,
I'VE BEEN KEEPING HIM COMPANY.
- OH, SORRY ABOUT THAT.
HEY, HAVE YOU GONE INSANE?
YOU KNOW YOU'RE NOT SUPPOSED TO
REVEAL YOURSELF
TO ANYONE BUT US!
( gasps )
- WELCOME BACK.
- HEY! IT'S THE EDITOR-IN-CHIEF!
WE'VE BEEN WORRYING
SICK ABOUT YOU, YOU KNOW THAT?
YOU COULD'VE AT LEAST
RETURNED OUR PHONE CALLS!
FOR ALL WE KNEW YOU
COULD HAVE BEEN INJURED
ON ONE OF YOUR
STORY ASSIGNMENTS.
EITHER THAT OR YOU
FINALLY CONVINCED HIROMI
TO RUN OFF WITH YOU
AND TIE THE KNOT.
- ARE YOU FINISHED?
- HEY, DON'T PRETEND LIKE
YOU DON'T AGREE WITH ME!
- KOUHEI, NOT ONLY DO YOU
HAVE THE SOCIAL GRACES
OF A BARNYARD ANIMAL,
YOU'VE SHOWN YOURSELF TO BE MORE
DENSE THAN I THOUGHT POSSIBLE.
- WHAT?
- HAVEN'T YOU NOTICED
ANYTHING PECULIAR?
- HEY! HE'S WEARING
GRANDPA'S WORK ROBE!
I DON'T GET IT, WHY IS THE
EDITOR IN GRANDPA'S CLOTHES?
- DO I REALLY HAVE TO
SPELL IT OUT FOR YOU?
- NOW I SEE!
YOU HAVE GOT GRANDPA!
- WHY YES, I'M HAPPY TO
REPORT THAT YOUR GRANDFATHER
HAS BEEN IN MY MASTER'S
CUSTODY FOR QUITE SOME TIME.
( laughing )
- WHO'S HE TALKING ABOUT?
- MY GUESS IS COUNT KINKEL.
- UH-OH.
- IT SEEMS HE'S TURNED THIS
POOR MAN INTO ONE OF HIS SLAVES.
- SO DO YOU THINK THAT'S WHAT
HAPPENED TO HIROMI?
- MOST LIKELY.
- MY MASTER SENT ME TO DELIVER
AN INVITATION FOR YOU
TO JOIN HIM AT HIS ESTATE.
ISN'T THAT WONDERFUL?
( laughing )
- ( lightning crashing )
- Kouhei: THAT'S THE HOUSE THAT
HAZUKI GREW UP IN, ISN'T IT?
- Editor: KOUHEI MORIOKA,
SEIJI MIDO,
AND THE CHILD ARE
INVITED TO ATTEND.
IN ADDITION, MY MASTER WISHES
TO EXTEND A WARNING.
SHOULD ANY OF YOU
CHOOSE TO DECLINE,
YOU WILL DO SO AT THE COST
OF YOUR GRANDFATHER'S LIFE!
- HUH?
- ( laughing )
- FOR ALL WE KNOW GRANDPA'S
AT THE HOSPITAL
RIGHT WHERE WE LEFT HIM AND
THIS IS JUST SOME LOUSY TRAP!
- DOUBTFUL. KINKEL'S TOO STRONG
TO RELY ON EMPTY THREATS,
AND THAT MEANS
WE'RE IN REAL TROUBLE.
THE OTHER NIGHT, WHEN WE HAD TO
FACE THE COUNT AT THE HOTEL,
THE ONLY REASON
WE SUCCEEDED WAS
BECAUSE WE HAD GRANDFATHER
AND ELFRIEDE'S HELP.
BUT NOT THIS TIME.
- WHAT ARE YOU TALKING
ABOUT? WE HAVE YOU!
THAT'S GOT TO COUNT
FOR SOMETHING, RIGHT?
- AS MUCH AS IT PAINS ME
TO ADMIT MY OWN SHORTCOMINGS,
THERE'S NO FEASIBLE WAY I COULD
DEFEAT A VAMPIRE LIKE KINKEL.
I KNOW IT'S NOT WHAT
YOU WANT TO HEAR
BUT GOING THERE
MEANS CERTAIN DEATH.
I'M SORRY. BUT THIS
JUST LOOKS HOPELESS.
- Hazuki: WELL
I'M GOING, ANYWAY.
I'LL GO ALONE IF I HAVE TO.
- YOU'RE AWAKE, MASTER.
- BUT YOU CAN'T GO!
- GRANDFATHER HAS ALWAYS
BEEN SO NICE TO ME,
EVEN WHEN I DIDN'T DESERVE IT.
HE'S SURE TREATED ME A HECK OF A
LOT BETTER THAN YOU TWO HAVE!
HE GAVE ME HAIJI, AND HE GAVE
ME THE BENEFIT OF THE DOUBT
WHEN NOBODY ELSE WOULD.
- MMM-HMM.
SO I'M GOING. AND I PROMISE,
KINKEL WILL PAY!
- THAT'S NOT VERY POLITE,
LITTLE GIRL.
MY MASTER WILL
HAVE TO PUNISH YOU.
( laughing )
- WHAT'S HE LAUGHING AT?
- JUDGING FROM HIS BEHAVIOR, THE
COUNT HAS PROBABLY ORDERED HIM
TO LAUGH HIMSELF TO DEATH AFTER
HE CARRIED OUT HIS MISSION,
BUT LUCKILY I KNOW A SPELL THAT
SHOULD STOP HIM
BEFORE HE SUCCEEDS.
AT LEAST I HOPE IT WILL.
I SUPPOSE KINKEL WOULD
ENJOY MAKING MINDLESS SLAVES
DESTROY THEMSELVES FOR HIS
OWN SADISTIC AMUSEMENT.
- I KNEW THERE WAS SOMETHING
ABOUT THE COUNT I DIDN'T LIKE.
- RIGHT. SO LET'S GO
MAKE HIM PAY.
- Seiji: IS IT TOO LATE
TO CHANGE MY MIND?
- I GUESS NOT. BUT IF YOU DID
YOU'D HAVE TO LOAN
ME YOUR CAR, YOU KNOW.
- WELL, IF THAT'S THE
CASE, KOUHEI, NEVER MIND.
I'VE SEEN WHAT YOU CALL DRIVING.
- HEY, KNOCK IT OFF, YOU'RE
GONNA GET IN TROUBLE
IF YOU SCUFF UP THOSE SEATS.
BESIDES, YOU SHOULDN'T HAVE FUN
WHILE YOUR MASTER'S
IN THE TRUNK.
YOU'LL JUST MAKE HER
FEEL WORSE.
- SHOWS HOW MUCH
YOU KNOW, SLAVE BOY.
MASTER TOLD ME SHE DOESN'T MIND
RIDING IN THE TRUNK
AS LONG AS IT'S NICE
AND CLEAN LIKE SEIJI'S
AND NOT OLD AND STINKY
LIKE YOURS IS.
- ( scoffs )
- I HATE THAT HIROMI
AND THE EDITOR-IN-CHIEF
HAD TO GET MIXED
UP IN ALL OF THIS.
I CAN'T HELP
BUT FEEL RESPONSIBLE.
- THAT'S ONE MORE REASON
WHY WE NEED TO DO SOMETHING!
- RIGHT?
- YEAH.
- ( lightning crashing )
- THAT'S WEIRD. THE
LAST TIME WE WERE HERE,
THE PLACE LOOKED CONDEMNED.
- I SUPPOSE HE WANTED TO MAKE IT
MORE SUITABLE FOR HIS GUESTS.
- YOU MEAN MORE SUITABLE
FOR HIS VICTIMS.
HEY, WHAT'S WITH THE BACKPACK?
- I FOUND IT IN THE STOREROOM.
DON'T YOU THINK IT'S CUTE?
- KILL ME, PLEASE.
- I'M WILLING TO BET IT'S
MORE THAN DECORATIVE. SEE?
STAKES, CROSSES,
GARLIC, HOLY WATER.
THESE THINGS COULD
COME IN HANDY,
ESPECIALLY CONSIDERING
OUR ADVERSARY.
SHE'S ACTUALLY PLANNING AHEAD.
- WELL, IF THEY'RE SO
FRICKING HANDY,
HOW COME LITTLE MISS
BLOODSUCKER HERE ISN'T AFFECTED?
- WOULDN'T YOU LIKE TO KNOW?
- IT'S PROBABLY 'CAUSE
YOUR SKIN'S THICK AS A RHINO'S.
- MY SKIN'S SOFT AS SILK,
THANK YOU VERY MUCH!
- ( gate creaking )
- ( all gasping )
- HIROMI, IS THAT YOU?
- MY MASTER HAS BEEN
EXPECTING YOU.
- ( thunder rumbling )
- PLEASE FEEL FREE TO
ENJOY SOME REFRESHMENTS.
- YUM! DON'T HAVE TO
ASK ME TWICE!
- HEY, WHAT IF THE FOOD'S
POISONOUS OR SOMETHING?
MAYBE SUPERNATURAL THINGS
LIKE SHIKIGAMI ARE IMMUNE TO IT.
- I BELIEVE POISON IS A LITTLE
TOO OBVIOUS FOR
THE COUNT'S TASTE.
I GET THE FEELING
THIS IS HIS VERSION
OF THE LAST SUPPER
BEFORE OUR CRUCIFIXION.
- YOUR SOUP HAS GOTTEN COLD.
SHALL I REHEAT IT?
WOULD YOU LIKE SOME BREAD
TO GO WITH YOUR MEAL?
I COULD BUTTER IT.
PERHAPS YOU WOULD LIKE
SOME ROASTED MEAT?
I COULD CUT IT FOR YOU.
AND THIS ONE'S THE SOY SAUCE,
SO MAKE SURE YOU DON'T
MIX THEM UP, OKAY?
HERE YOU GO, HAZUKI,
YOUR FIRST COMMISSION.
HEY? WHAT'S WITH THE SAD FACE?
I GO TO ALL THIS TROUBLE
FOR MY CUTE LITTLE FRIEND,
DESPITE MY INSANE WORK SCHEDULE,
AND SHE JUST LOOKS AT ME
LIKE I'VE RIPPED HER HEART OUT.
- HIROMI, ARE YOU
STILL IN THERE?
- WOULD MISTRESS LUNA
PREFER DESSERT INSTEAD?
- ( crackling )
- ( gasps )
- YOUR GRANDFATHER
TASTED THIS DESSERT AS WELL.
I HOPE YOU ENJOY IT,
IT'S MY SPECIALTY.
- HIROMI!
- BIG SISTER!
I'LL GET YOU BACK TO NORMAL.
I PROMISE I WILL, HIROMI.
JUST HOLD ON!
- WHAT THE HELL?
WHY DID SHE HURT HERSELF?
- I TOLD YOU. THAT'S THE WAY
THE COUNT OPERATES.
- MONSTER.
( gasps )
- PLEASE FOLLOW ME THIS WAY.
MY MASTER IS WAITING.
- MAN. DIDN'T LOOK THIS BIG
FROM THE OUTSIDE.
SO, YOU REALLY
USED TO LIVE HERE, BRAT?
- MMM-HMM.
- SEIJI, HAVE YOU BEEN ABLE
TO SENSE WHERE GRANDPA IS YET?
- SORT OF. I CAN TELL HE'S NEAR.
BUT FOR SOME REASON I'M NOT ABLE
TO PINPOINT HIS EXACT LOCATION.
- WHAT IS IT, HAZUKI?
- OH, IT'S NOTHING.
- PLEASE MAKE
YOURSELVES COMFORTABLE.
- NO! DON'T GO, HIROMI!
- YOU GOT WHAT YOU WANTED,
NOW SHOW YOURSELF KINKEL!
WHERE'S MY GRANDFATHER, DAMN IT?
GRAMPS, CAN YOU
HEAR ME? GRAMPS?
- THIS BED...
( laughing )
HUNGRY! HUNGRY, MAMA!
IT WAS HERE.
I LIVED IN THIS ROOM WITH
MY MOTHER WHEN I WAS LITTLE.
- YEAH. THIS MUST BE HARD.
- IT IS.
I REMEMBER SO MUCH.
- SO, WHAT DO YOU KNOW
ABOUT THESE PAINTINGS OVER HERE?
- I DON'T THINK I'VE EVER
SEEN THEM BEFORE.
- ( all gasp )
- WHAT IS THIS?
- Woman: THEY'RE GLIMPSES
INTO THE REALITY
THAT WILL FALL
UPON YOU VERY SOON.
- ( gasps )
MAMA?
STOP IT! IT'S NOT FAIR!
IT'S NOT REAL! YOU'RE USING
HER IMAGE TO TRICK ME!
- COME ON KINKEL! STOP BEING
A COWARD AND SHOW YOURSELF!
- ( chuckles )
- COME ON!
I'M NOT PLAYING AROUND!
- AM I TO UNDERSTAND THAT YOU'RE
THREATENING ME, KOUHEI MORIOKA?
- MAYBE!
- REALLY, MISTRESS LUNA,
WHY DO YOU WASTE YOUR
TIME ON THIS HALF-WIT?
CAN'T YOU SEE? A MAN LIKE HIM
CAN ONLY BRING RUIN TO OUR KIND.
HIS POISONED BLOOD ROBS YOU OF
THE VERY ESSENCE OF WHO YOU ARE.
IT NUMBS YOU.
BY ATTACHING YOURSELF TO HIM
YOU DENY YOUR TRUE EXISTENCE
FOR AN INFERIOR LIFE
PLAGUED BY MEDIOCRITY.
THIRST MAKES YOU EXTRAORDINARY.
OUR THIRST SEPARATES US FROM
THE RANKS OF POWERLESS MORTALS.
THAT MAN IS AN EVIL DREAM
WHICH BREAKS THE PEACE
OF OUR DIVINE SLUMBER.
PLEASE, AWAKEN FROM THIS
NIGHTMARE AND COME HOME TO ME.
- YOU'RE THE NIGHTMARE,
NOT KOUHEI.
PREPARE YOURSELF,
BECAUSE I'LL NEVER FORGIVE
YOU FOR WHAT YOU'VE DONE!
- IS THAT SO?
THEN TELL ME, WHAT
SORT OF PREPARATIONS
DO YOU SUGGEST I MAKE?
- ( exclaims )
THAT ISN'T SEIJI!
THAT'S KINKEL!
- BUT HOW? HE CAN'T BE!
- ( laughs ) YOU REALLY ARE
AS STUPID AS YOU LOOK!
- HAIJI, ATTACK!
- HAIJI!
- ( laughs ) WELL,
THAT'S TOO BAD.
IT APPEARS I JUST KNOCKED
YOUR SHIKIGAMI SENSELESS.
I MEANT TO DO
A LOT WORSE THAN THAT.
- OH, YEAH? WELL YOU'RE
WEAKER THAN YOU THINK!
- ( screams )
- KOUHEI!
- I'M FINE. COME ON!
- WE HAVE TO BE CAREFUL.
THE COUNT'S PRETTY SNEAKY.
- OH, REALLY, YOU DON'T SAY.
- ( both exclaim )
- ( yelling )
- HAZUKI!
( groans )
I...
I KNOW YOU'RE NOT SEIJI!
WHOA! OKAY!
STOP! TIME OUT!
- KOUHEI!
- ( yelling )
NOW, WHERE IS HE?
WHERE'S MY GRANDPA?
- HOW SHOULD I KNOW?
YOU'RE THE ONE WHO LOCKED
HIM UP IN HERE, AREN'T YOU?
- WHAT? I DON'T
EVEN UNDERSTAND
WHAT GAMES YOU'RE
PLAYING ANYMORE.
BUT HEY, IF YOU REALLY
WANT A CHALLENGE,
THEN HOW'S THIS FOR A GAME?
- GOYO HAKKE!
- KOUHEI!
- ( screaming ) NO!
HAZUKI! NO, PLEASE! JUST LET
GO OF ME AND GET OUT OF HERE!
- WOULD YOU STOP TELLING ME
WHAT TO DO? AND GO ON A DIET!
- WAIT, IS IT REALLY YOU?
YOU SEEM GENUINE.
TELL ME, ARE YOU THE REAL
KOUHEI AND THE REAL HAZUKI?
- WELL, OF COURSE IT'S US!
- WHO ELSE WOULD WE BE?
- I SEE. NO WONDER MY SPELLS
WOULDN'T WORK ON YOU.
- OH, NO WAY. YOU GET AWAY
FROM US, VAMPIRE SCUM!
- FROM WHAT I CAN TELL
COUNT KINKEL TRICKED US
INTO TURNING ON EACH OTHER.
- HE'S GONNA ATTACK AGAIN!
- HIDE SOMEWHERE!
- WOULD YOU SHUT UP
- OR BITE HIM! OR SOMETHING!
- FOR A MINUTE?
- A SMART BOY.
- ( groans )
- I'M SURE YOU'VE
REALIZED IT BY NOW.
I HAVE A UNIQUE TALENT
THAT ALLOWS ME TO BEND
AND MANIPULATE LIGHT.
BEFORE YOU WERE EVEN AWARE
SOMETHING WAS AMISS,
YOU HAD ENTERED INTO AN
ILLUSION OF MY OWN CREATION.
- THE MANIPULATION
OF LIGHT. OF COURSE!
THAT'S WHAT I FELT
IN THE HALL!
YOU SEPARATED US IN THAT MOMENT.
TAKING US DOWN
TWO SEPARATE PATHS,
REPLACING MY COMPANIONS
WITH MIRAGES.
- I CONFESS, IT WAS
DIFFICULT TO PULL OFF.
IT'S NOT EASY BEING
IN TWO PLACES AT ONCE.
- WHEN YOU BROUGHT
US BACK TOGETHER
WE THOUGHT WE WERE
STILL FIGHTING YOU.
AND WE ALMOST KILLED
EACH OTHER AS A RESULT.
I SHOULD HAVE KNOWN YOU
WOULD STOOP SO LOW.
- UNFORTUNATELY IT
WASN'T LOW ENOUGH.
- ( groans )
- HEY! GET YOUR NASTY
FEET OFF MY SLAVE!
- THAT'S NOT A VERY NICE
THING TO SAY, MISTRESS.
ACTUALLY, I RECENTLY HAD
THESE SHOES POLISHED.
HIROMI DOES EXCELLENT WORK.
AH, YES. WHEN YOU GLARE
AT ME WITH THOSE EYES
I FEEL EXCITEMENT PULSE
THROUGH MY ENTIRE BODY!
- KOUHEI, HERE!
- WELL, THAT COULD
HAVE BEEN WORSE. I'M NOT DEAD.
- GOOD THING.
- GET AWAY FROM HIM,
MISTRESS LUNA!
- I WARNED YOU!
NOW, PREPARE YOURSELF!
KINKEL!
- THIS CAN'T BE HER POWER!
DAMN YOU. VAMPIRE'S LOVER!
- ( sighs )
- YOU OKAY?
- DO YOU THINK THAT'S
THE LAST OF HIM?
THAT'S PROBABLY TOO MUCH
TO HOPE FOR, HUH?
- THE COUNT MAY BE
GONE FOR THE MOMENT
BUT I WOULDN'T LET YOUR
GUARD DOWN IF I WERE YOU.
HE TRICKS YOU INTO A
FALSE SENSE OF SECURITY
SO HE CAN CATCH YOU
AT YOUR WEAKEST.
- MAYBE SO, BUT I
DON'T THINK HE'LL BE
BOTHERING US FOR A WHILE.
- WHY IS THAT?
- TAKE A LOOK AT THE SKY.
- OH, GOOD POINT.
IT IS ALMOST DAYBREAK.
- ( bell ringing )
- ( gasps )
- GRANDPA!
- Seiji: WHAT'S HE DONE TO HIM?
- Kouhei: OKAY LISTEN, YOU TAKE
THE BRAT AND GO FIND HIROMI.
I'M GONNA GO CUT GRANDPA DOWN SO
WE CAN GET THE HELL
OUT OF THIS PLACE!
GRANDPA!
- HIROMI?
- HIROMI!
- ( muffled cries )
- ELFRIEDE!
- SHE'S RIGHT BY THE WINDOW.
SHE WON'T LAST LONG.
- ( muffled cries )
- THIS MIGHT NOT BE SMART.
BUT WE CAN'T JUST LEAVE HER.
- GRANDPA!
- ( coughing )
YOU'VE GOT TO STOP KOUHEI!
IT'S KINKEL!
HE'S... HE'S...
A DAYWALKER!
- ( theme music playing )
- ( singing in Japanese )
- BIG BROTHER! I'M HUNGRY.
WHAT DO YOU WANNA EAT?
OH, WAIT. WE HAVE TO DO
THE RIDDLE FIRST.
UM, LET'S SEE.
OOH! I GOT IT!
WHAT'S A VAMPIRE'S
FAVORITE FOOD?
( laughs ) I LIKE THIS ONE.
FULL, FULL, FULL MOON!
WHAT'S A VAMPIRE'S
FAVORITE FOOD?
GRAVE-Y.
( laughs ) OH, SHUT UP.
IT'S FUNNY.
NEXT TIME ON MOON PHASE.
EPISODE 13.
"LET'S DEFEAT THE COUNT!"
YOU REALLY DON'T THINK
THAT ONE'S FUNNY?