- Hikaru: YOU KNOW YOU'RE JUST
WASTING YOUR TIME, YOU FREAKS!
- IT'S PRETTY!
- HELLO! ARE YOU LISTENING?
- SO PRETTY.
- Vargas: YES. THEY HAVE GOOD
FIREWORKS IN JAPAN.
- DON'T YOU EVEN
REALIZE HOW STUPID IT IS
TO MESS WITH
THE MIDO CLAN?
YOU FANG-FACES BETTER LET
ME GO WHILE THERE'S TIME,
OR IT'S GONNA BE THE LAST
MISTAKE YOU EVER MAKE!
- ( snarling )
- YEAH. YOU HEARD ME!
- QUIET, HUMAN!
YOU'RE DISTURBING THE PRINCESS.
- NOW TELL ME, PRINCESS ARTE,
WHERE DID YOU GET
THOSE CAT EARS?
- JEDA GAVE THEM TO ME.
- WHAT CAN I SAY?
I'M A SENTIMENTALIST AT HEART.
- Vargas: THERE YOU ARE, JEDA.
- HOW ARE THOSE EYES
OF YOURS, MR. VARGAS?
- I'M FINE. ANY PROGRESS
WITH YOUR SURVEILLANCE?
- NO, NOT REALLY.
I JUST FELT LIKE TAKING A WALK.
- IS THAT YOUR IDEA OF A JOKE?
- Arte: CAN I KILL LUNA NOW?
I WANT TO.
LET ME KILL HER.
- Jeda: SOUNDS FUN
TO ME, PRINCESS.
BUT I'M AFRAID IT WOULD GIVE
OUR MASTER QUITE THE FROWN.
- THEN GIVE ME THIS ONE.
I WANNA KILL HIM INSTEAD.
AND LUNA CAN WATCH.
- ( theme song playing )
( singing in Japanese )
- ( Hazuki sighing )
- OKEY-DOKE, MASTER!
FOOD'S HERE!
GRANDMA KOHARU MADE
THE BIG ONES!
AND THE LITTLE ONES WERE ALL ME!
THEY'RE ALL BITE-SIZED
AND EASY TO EAT!
I COULDN'T FIT THE PICKLED
PLUMBS IN THE MIDDLE
SO I USED CINNAMON CAKE INSTEAD!
THE CINNAMON MAKES ME SNEEZE
BUT THEY TASTE REALLY GREAT!
- THANKS, HAIJI. BUT NOT
NOW, I'M NOT HUNGRY.
- BUT THEY'RE YUMMY, MASTER!
- Kouhei: EAT THEM.
- KOUHEI.
- COME ON, YA
HAVEN'T HAD ANYTHING
SINCE WE GOT BACK LAST NIGHT.
THAT'S JUST NOT HEALTHY.
- I DON'T FEEL LIKE FOOD.
- MMM. THIS ONE'S GOT FISH.
MAN THAT'S GOOD!
- ( stomach growling )
- SOUNDS LIKE YOUR
STOMACH'S MORE HONEST
THAN YOUR MOUTH, HAZ.
- DON'T BE STUPID!
- HERE.
HEY, HAIJI,
GRAB SOME TEA, WOULD YA?
- YOU BET, SLAVE-BOY!
OPERATION TEA RETRIEVAL!
- COME ON.
- UM.
HIKARU, I BET SHE'S
HUNGRY TOO.
- OH, HAZ.
- IT'S MY FAULT.
I'M A PLAGUE.
- ( wind blowing )
- THAT AGAIN?
SERIOUSLY, YOU NEED TO SHUT UP.
- WHA... EXCUSE ME?
- THERE'S NO POINT IN
DWELLING ON REGRETS
AND HATING YOURSELF NOW.
YOU'LL HAVE PLENTY OF TIME
TO DO THAT LATER.
RIGHT NOW YOU NEED
TO EAT AND REST UP
SO YOU'LL BE READY TO
RESCUE HIKARU WHEN IT'S TIME.
OTHERWISE YOU'RE GONNA BE
TOO WEAK TO HELP
AND YOU'LL FEEL EVEN MORE
PATHETIC AND MISERABLE.
IT'S THE ONLY APPROACH
THAT MAKES SENSE.
RIGHT?
- HM.
- ( Kouhei clears throat )
OKAY, WHERE'S THE TEA?
- OOPSIE, IT SLIPPED.
- OH! HOT!
- I'M SO CLUMSY.
IT DROPPED RIGHT OUT OF
MY FINGERS. IMAGINE THAT!
HEY! HOLD ON!
YOU DID THAT ON...
( groaning )
YOU SHOULD BE MORE CAREFUL,
SLAVE BOY! YOU'LL HURT YOURSELF!
- ( Hazuki giggling )
- ( Kouhei groaning )
- LOOK AT THAT!
MASTER'S LAUGHING!
- HOW'S A GIRL SUPPOSED
TO BROOD PROPERLY
WHEN YOU'RE SPILLING TEA
ALL OVER THE PLACE?
- SO IT'S MY FAULT?
- SURE! JUST LIKE IT
ALWAYS IS, SLAVE BOY!
- CAN IT!
- ( Hazuki giggling )
- I GUESS THE IMPORTANT THING
IS YOU'RE EATING AGAIN, RIGHT?
THOUGH IF YOU WANT TEA,
YOU'LL HAVE TO DRINK MY HAIR.
- Hazuki: NO. I'M GOOD.
- Yayoi: ARE YOU SURE
ABOUT THIS?
- Ryuuhei: I REALIZE THE RISK,
IF THAT'S WHAT YOU MEAN.
- KOUHEI HAS MATURED REMARKABLY
IN THE LAST EIGHT
MONTHS NO DOUBT.
BUT WHAT YOU'RE ASKING...
- EVEN WITH HIS PROGRESS,
THERE'S LITTLE CHANCE
HE'LL BE ABLE TO
COMPLETELY ACCEPT IT NOW.
I KNOW THAT.
UNFORTUNATELY, WE'RE OUT
OF TIME AND WE HAVE TO TRY.
- IF IT'S REALLY OUR
ONLY CHOICE, SO BE IT.
I JUST HOPE YOU CAN LIVE
WITH THE RESULTS.
- I'M SURPRISED YOU'RE BEING
SO SOFT, MASTER YAYOI.
HE'S NOT A CHILD ANYMORE.
AND THERE IS EVIL THREATENING
THE GIRL HE'S CHOSEN TO PROTECT.
HE CANNOT BE SHIELDED FOREVER.
WE'LL NEVER BE SAFE FROM THEM
IF WE'RE AFRAID TO TAKE A RISK.
YOU KNOW THAT'S TRUE.
- THEN IT'S DECIDED.
- AND WHAT ABOUT KOJIRO?
HE'S NOT EVEN HERE.
I MUST SAY I'M HESITANT
TO GO THROUGH WITH THIS
WITHOUT HIS BLESSING.
AFTER ALL, HE IS THE HEAD
OF THE MIDO CLAN.
- WE DON'T HAVE TIME.
- VERY WELL.
I'LL TALK TO KOUHEI TODAY.
- HEY!
WHAT ARE YOU DOING OVER HERE?
- UH, NOTHING.
- WELL I'VE GOT A QUESTION
FOR YOU, MISTER!
- YOU DO?
- HOW COME YOU DIDN'T
GO AFTER THE VAMPIRES
INSTEAD OF COMING BACK
WITH THE OTHERS?
YOU COULD'VE PICKED
UP THEIR TRAIL IF YOU WANTED!
- I DON'T KNOW, HAIJI.
BECAUSE I THOUGHT WE NEEDED TO
COME UP WITH A
DECENT PLAN FIRST.
I DIDN'T THINK IT WOULD HELP
US MUCH IF I GET CAPTURED TOO.
- SOUNDS LIKE AN AWFULLY
LOGICAL THOUGHT
FOR SOMEONE WHOSE FIANCEE
WAS JUST KIDNAPPED!
I THINK THE REAL REASON IS
'CAUSE YOU WERE TOO SCARED TO!
I DON'T BLAME YOU, THEY WERE
PRETTY SCARY GUYS.
I PROB'LY WOULD'VE
CHICKENED OUT TOO!
- ( agitated ) YOU'RE WRONG!
THAT'S NOT THE REASON.
- UH-OH. MAYBE I WENT
A LITTLE TOO FAR.
- HM.
- THANKS!
- WE'LL SEND YOU A COPY!
WELL THAT TOOK A LOT LESS
TIME THAN WE THOUGHT.
- I THINK WE GOT SOME
PRETTY GOOD SHOTS, TOO.
- IF THINGS KEEP GOING
THIS SMOOTHLY,
WE MIGHT HAVE SOME
FREE TIME ON OUR LAST DAY.
- HMM. SIGHTSEEING IN KYOTO?
YEAH, I THINK I CAN DEAL
WITH THAT.
- ( thinking ) MAYBE I SHOULD
CHECK IT OUT.
- Kouhei: I HAVE JAGAN?
- HM.
- WHAT IS JAGAN?
- IT'S ONE OF THE MOST
POWERFUL PSYCHIC GIFTS.
A KIND OF SUPERNATURAL EYE
THAT ALLOWS HIM TO
NOT ONLY SEE SPIRITS,
BUT DESTROY THEM.
- A POWERFUL PSYCHIC?
THIS KOUHEI?
NO WAY.
HE'S LIKE THE MOST PSYCHICALLY
DENSE PERSON ON THE PLANET.
- WE DID THAT.
WE REALIZED YOU POSSESSED JAGAN
SHORTLY AFTER YOU WERE BORN.
FROM THE START OF YOUR LIFE,
YOU COULD SEE OUR WORLD
AND THE SUPERNATURAL PLANE
IN THE EXACT SAME WAY.
EVEN THE FIERCEST DEMONS
THAT ESCAPED OUR DETECTION
WERE CLEAR TO YOU.
AFTER DELIBERATION, OUR
FAMILY MADE THE DECISION
TO SEAL YOUR POWER
FOR YOUR OWN GOOD.
TO ACCOMPLISH THIS WE
BLOCKED THE PSYCHIC CHANNEL
THAT CONNECTED YOUR
JAGAN TO YOUR MIND
AND MADE YOU UNABLE
TO NOTICE THE SUPERNATURAL PLANE
THROUGH THE POWER OF KOTODAMA.
- WHAT'S KOTODAMA?
IT'S THE SPIRITUAL POWER
IN WORDS,
THE BELIEF THAT SPEAKING
A THOUGHT BREATHES LIFE INTO IT.
KOUHEI, DO YOU REMEMBER BEING
TOLD OVER AND OVER
THAT YOU HAD NO PSYCHIC POWER?
- BUT, WHY WOULD YOU
DO THAT TO HIM?
- TRY TO PICTURE IT.
A CHILD IN CONSTANT CONTACT
WITH THE SUPERNATURAL,
SEEMING TO TALK TO EMPTY SPACES,
WARNING OF DEMONS NO
ONE ELSE COULD SEE.
PEOPLE WOULD FEAR AND MOCK HIM,
TURN HIM INTO AN OUTCAST.
BUT THAT'S NOT ALL.
PSYCHICS AND SPIRITS
ATTRACT EACH OTHER.
IF HE SAW THEM, THEY
COULD SEE HIM TOO.
WE WERE AFRAID HE'D BE
ATTACKED, OR POSSESSED.
WE WERE ONLY TRYING TO KEEP
YOU SAFE FROM HARM, KOUHEI.
- Ryuuhei: KOUHEI, DON'T LOOK!
TURN AROUND AND START WALKING!
- WHAT IS IT, GRANDFATHER?
I WANNA SEE IT TOO!
- IT'S NOTHING!
COME ON, WE'RE GOING HOME.
- LET GO!
- KOUHEI!
- COME BACK!
- THERE'S NOTHING!
WHAT'RE YOU GUYS MAKING
SUCH A BIG FUSS ABOUT?
- THAT'S RIGHT.
I NEVER COULD SEE ANYTHING.
AND THAT ALWAYS MADE ME FEEL
LIKE AN OUTCAST, TOO.
- KOUHEI.
- ALL THESE YEARS OF LIES.
HE NEVER KNEW
WHAT HE HAD.
- ( growling and snarling )
- THERE'S NOTHING!
WHAT'RE YOU GUYS
MAKING SUCH A BIG FUSS ABOUT?
- ( roaring )
- ( snarling )
- Seiji: "THERE'S NOTHING."
THAT'S ALL HE HAD TO SAY AND
THOSE DEMONS WERE DESTROYED.
THAT'S THE SHEER POWER
OF HIS JAGAN.
IN ALL MY YEARS OF STUDY,
I'VE NEVER GOTTEN CLOSE TO THAT.
IT'S A TALENT YOU HAVE
TO BE BORN WITH.
WHY?
WHY IS HE THE ONLY ONE?
- Kouhei: REMOVE THE SEAL.
I WANNA SAVE HIKARU.
BESIDES, I'D RATHER BE THE ONE
TO FIGHT WITH ARTE
INSTEAD OF HAZUKI.
I MEAN, IF THAT GIRL REALLY
IS HER HALF SISTER.
- KOUHEI.
- IF THAT'S YOUR CHOICE,
I'LL REMOVE IT.
BUT I WANT TO MAKE
SURE YOU UNDERSTAND
WHAT YOU'RE AGREEING TO.
JAGAN IS LIKE A VIOLENT TIGER,
AND CONTROLLING IT
TAKES GREAT MENTAL STRENGTH.
NO ONE FROM THE MIDO CLAN HAS
EVER BEEN ABLE TO
DO IT SUCCESSFULLY.
YOU WILL SUFFER.
ARE YOU WILLING TO
RISK YOUR HEALTH,
YOUR SANITY, EVEN YOUR LIFE?
- HIS LIFE?
- YES.
- ( gasping )
- THEN WE'LL PROCEED
WITH ONE MORE DEMAND.
ONCE I'VE REMOVED THE SEAL,
YOU'RE FORBIDDEN TO SEE HAZUKI
UNTIL YOU HAVE FULL
CONTROL OF YOUR JAGAN POWER.
- WHAT?
- YES, I UNDERSTAND.
- WAIT! BUT MASTER,
IF THIS IS GONNA HURT HIM
LET ME STAY AT HIS SIDE SO I
CAN HELP TAKE CARE OF HIM!
- YOU CAN'T.
- I WANNA KNOW WHY!
- HAZUKI, STOP!
THANK YOU. I ACCEPT.
- THIS WILL HURT.
- I'M READY.
- ( gasping )
- ( Kouhei screaming )
- ( Hazuki panting )
- I KNOW THIS IS HARD,
DEAR, BUT BE PATIENT.
- OH.
WONDER WHAT TIME IT IS.
MUST'VE PASSED OUT
FROM THE PAIN.
MAN, IT STILL HURTS.
- WANT SOME HELP?
- HEY, HOW'S IT GOIN'?
THAT YOU, HAZ?
OH, KAORU.
( sighs ) I'M SORRY.
- THAT'S OKAY. HERE.
- THANKS. THAT'S NICE.
- ( giggles )
- I CAN'T STAND THIS!
HOW COME KAORU GETS TO SEE HIM
AND I DON'T? IT MAKES NO SENSE!
- COULD IT HAVE ANYTHING TO DO
WITH YOUR TEMPER?
- WHAT DID YOU SAY?
- ( screaming )
- THAT'S IT!
I'M SEEING HIM!
- MASTER, YOU CAN'T!
- Yayoi: I'M COUNTING
ON YOU, KAORU.
- I KNOW.
- ( Kouhei screams )
WHAT'S GOING ON?
- SO YOU SEE THEM?
- HEY, KAORU, WHAT ARE THEY?
- DEMONIC SPIRITS.
- OH, IS THAT ALL?
OH, MAN! I'VE NEVER BEEN ABLE
TO SEE 'EM THIS CLEARLY BEFORE.
- ( spirits growling )
- ( Kouhei whimpering )
HEY. WHERE'RE YOU GOING?
- Yayoi: TRY TO MAKE
THEM VANISH.
- HUH?
- UP TO THIS POINT YOU'VE BEEN
USING YOUR POWER UNCONSCIOUSLY
TO MAKE DEMONS THAT THREATENED
YOU DISAPPEAR, KOUHEI.
NOW YOU MUST LEARN TO DO IT
CONSCIOUSLY, ON COMMAND.
- MAKE THEM VANISH?
DOING WHAT?
- USE YOUR MIND, KOUHEI.
- AND WILL THEM
OUT OF EXISTENCE.
- WILL THEM, HUH?
- ( snarling )
- ( screaming )
- THIS IS IMPOSSIBLE! I JUST
GOT MY POWERS TODAY!
- YOU FOOL.
DON'T RUN FROM THEM.
- BUT, MASTER!
CUT ME SOME SLACK!
- THIS IS IMPOSSIBLE! I JUST
GOT MY POWERS TODAY!
- YOU FOOL.
DON'T RUN FROM THEM.
- BUT, MASTER!
CUT ME SOME SLACK!
- THIS IS IMPOSSIBLE! I JUST
GOT MY POWERS TODAY!
- YOU FOOL.
DON'T RUN FROM THEM.
- AREN'T YOU LISTENING?
I SAID CUT ME SOME SLACK!
- KAORU, DON'T!
I'M NOT JUST GONNA STAND HERE
AND WATCH WHILE BROTHER
KOUHEI GETS HURT.
MAYBE WE ARE PUSHING
HIM TOO QUICKLY.
I'M THE ONE WHO SUMMONED THEM,
AND IF ANYONE'S GONNA GET
HURT I'D RATHER IT BE ME.
- NO!
- KAORU.
- ( cackling )
- LEAVE HER ALONE!
- ( growling )
- DAMN IT!
( shouts ) JUST...
GO...
AWAY!
- ARE YOU ALL RIGHT?
- I'M FINE. AND I'M SORRY.
- YOU DID WHAT WAS NECESSARY.
JUST DON'T PUSH YOURSELF
TOO HARD, EITHER.
THIS ISN'T EASY WORK.
- I DON'T MIND. I LIKE
WORKING WITH KOUHEI.
- YOU DID WELL.
- I GUESS I AM A BIT TIRED.
- OKAY. NOW'S MY CHANCE!
( Hazuki giggling )
( screaming )
- WOW. LOOKS LIKE
A BARRIER SPELL.
- NO FAIR! MASTER YAYOI IS
A BIG, FRICKIN' MEANIE!
- ( yawning )
I'M GLAD THAT WORKED
AND ALL, BUT I'M BEAT.
I THINK I COULD
SLEEP FOR A WEEK.
- WHY CAN'T I SEE HIM?
- AH! WHAT A SPECTACULAR DAY!
- YEAH.
- KOUHEI'S DOING REALLY WELL.
HE'S BEEN IN THERE
FOR THREE DAYS!
HE'S LIKE COMPLETELY DIFFERENT
THAN HE WAS AT THE OLD HOUSE.
- WE SURE HAD FUN THERE, HUH?
- YOU BETCHA!
LOTS OF LAUGHS!
- IT WAS ALL THANKS TO HIM.
- HM?
- KOUHEI FREED ME AND
BROUGHT ME TO YOU GUYS.
HE'S MADE MY LIFE
SO MUCH BETTER.
- HAZUKI, DEAR.
THERE WILL COME A TIME
WHEN YOU WILL FIND
SOMEONE WHO YOU TRULY LOVE.
WHEN THAT DAY ARRIVES,
YOU MUST NOT SEAL THE
BLOOD PACT WITH HIM.
DO YOU UNDERSTAND?
NEVER WITH THE ONE YOU LOVE.
- BUT IT'S TOO LATE.
I ALREADY DID.
- Ryuuhei: IT MUST BE HARD
FOR HER, POOR CHILD.
BUT THE GREATEST PAINS
ARE YET TO COME.
- Vargas: WELL,
WHAT DO WE HAVE HERE?
- ( gasping )
- ( both gasping )
- MY GOD! WHAT HAPPENED HERE?
- ( swishing )
- ( grunting )
( grunting )
I THINK I'M STARTIN' TO
GET THE HANG OF IT.
( gasping )
- EAT 'EM WHEN YOU GET TIRED.
HANG IN THERE, ALL RIGHT?
- HAZUKI?
- KOUHEI!
- I THOUGHT THAT WAS YOU.
- HOW COULD YOU TELL?
- WELL, I DIDN'T FIGURE ANYBODY
ELSE'D BE VISITING ME RIGHT NOW.
YOU KEEP PRETTY LATE HOURS.
HOW'S LIFE?
- UM, OKAY, I GUESS.
HOW ABOUT YOU, DON'T YOU
GET BORED IN THERE?
- THEY KEEP ME BUSY.
- THAT'S GOOD. I WORRY.
- I'M GETTING A LOT BETTER AT
CONTROLLING MY POWER, THOUGH.
SHOULD BE OUTTA HERE
SOONER THAN I THOUGHT.
HAZUKI? YOU THERE?
- I'M SORRY.
- FOR WHAT?
- I'M USELESS. I'M NOT DOING
ANYTHING TO HELP.
- AH, COME ON.
- BUT IT'S TRUE.
- IS NOT! DON'T YOU REALIZE?
YOU'RE HELPING ME A LOT
MORE THAN ANYBODY ELSE IS.
YOU'RE WHAT KEEPS ME GOING
THROUGH ALL THE HARD STUFF.
( smirks ) AFTER ALL,
I GOTTA BE A GOOD SLAVE.
- KOUHEI...
I MISS YOU, THOUGH.
- YEAH. BUT RULES ARE RULES.
- SURE, I KNOW.
WELL HAVE A GOOD NIGHT, OKAY?
- YOU KNOW, ACTUALLY,
I AM DUE FOR A BATHROOM BREAK.
AND SINCE THERE'S
NOT ONE IN HERE,
I'LL HAVE TO MAKE MY WAY ACROSS
THE MAIN DECK IN A SECOND.
IF I HAPPEN TO RUN INTO
SOMEONE WHILE I'M OUT THERE,
I DON'T SEE HOW
THAT'S MY FAULT.
- OH, THAT'S TRUE! I SEE HOW
THAT COULD HAPPEN ACCIDENTALLY.
- WELL, IT'S BEEN GREAT TALKIN'
TO YA, I'VE GOTTA GO NOW.
- I'LL SEE YOU LATER, HAZUKI!
- HI, KOUHEI!
( gasping )
WHAT'S WRONG WITH YOU?
YOU'RE TREMBLING, KOUHEI.
- GET BACK!
- WHAT ARE YOU TALKING
ABOUT? IT'S ME. HAZUKI.
- DON'T TOUCH ME!
- KOUHEI?
- PLEASE GET BACK!
YOU'RE A MONSTER!
- ( bell ringing )
- ( theme song playing )
( singing in Japanese )
- Arte: FORGET LUNA. YOU'LL DO
RIDDLES WITH ME NOW.
WHAT STARTS WITH T, ENDS
WITH T, AND IS FULL OF TEA?
FULL, FULL, FULL, MOON.
THE ANSWER'S A TEAPOT.
THERE. WASN'T THAT MORE FUN?
WELL YOU BETTER LIKE IT,
BECAUSE YOU'LL KEEP PLAYING
WITH ME UNTIL YOU'RE DEAD.
NEXT TIME,
"BIG BROTHER, AM I THAT SCARY?"
I'M GOING TO BED NOW.
SING THE NURSERY RHYME
UNTIL I FALL ASLEEP, OKAY?