- ( she gasps )
- Hazuki: I'LL GO WITH YOU NOW.
BACK TO "MY KIND."
- WHAT IS THAT?
- IT'S A CASTLE.
- THAT'S SCHWARTZ QUELLE,
THE PLACE WHERE HAZUKI WAS
IMPRISONED WHEN
KOUHEI RESCUED HER.
- HOW'D IT GET HERE?
- THE CASTLE SEEKS MISTRESS LUNA
JUST AS SHE SEEKS THE CASTLE.
HER DECISION TO RETURN BROUGHT
IT FROM GERMANY TO HERE.
IT WILL APPEAR FOR HER ALWAYS.
WHENEVER SHE CHOOSES
FOR IT TO COME.
- WHAT'S HAPPENING NOW?
- IT SEEMS JEDA HAS
ACCOMPLISHED HIS MISSION.
YOU SHOULD BE PLEASED, HUMAN.
YOU'RE FREE TO GO.
- SERIOUSLY?
- AS PROMISED. WE HAVE WHAT WE
WANT. FOLLOW ME, PRINCESS.
- ( theme song playing )
- ( singing in Japanese )
- GOOD-BYE BIG BROTHER.
I'M GOING BACK? I'M
REALLY GOING BACK?
- I'M SORRY, MOTHER,
BUT I HAD TO COME BACK.
I KNOW YOU'LL UNDERSTAND.
I JUST REALLY WISH I COULD'VE
WAITED UNTIL I SAW YOU AGAIN.
AT LEAST ONCE.
- KOUHEI.
- YOU... I SAW YOU.
DO... DO YOU HAVE A NAME?
- WELL, OF COURSE I DO, SILLY.
MY NAME IS HAZUKI.
IT'S A PLEASURE TO MEET YOU.
AND WHAT'S YOUR NAME,
IF I MAY ASK?
- OH. YEAH, I'M KOUHEI MORIOKA.
- KOUHEI.
YOU'RE MY BIG BROTHER, KOUHEI.
I REMEMBER ALL OF IT.
LIKE IT JUST HAPPENED.
MY BIG BROTHER.
THAT WAS OUR FIRST KISS.
AND NOW IT'S ALL
GONNA BE OVER, BIG BROTHER.
I WANTED TO STAY
WITH YOU FOREVER,
EVEN IF YOU WERE A BAD SLAVE.
AND NOW I DON'T THINK
I'LL EVER GET TO SEE YOU AGAIN.
- ( sobbing )
- YOU'RE AFRAID OF ME.
I UNDERSTAND.
BUT DON'T WORRY,
IT'LL BE OVER SOON.
YOU DON'T HAVE TO BE AFRAID.
- YOU DON'T HAVE TO BE AFRAID
OF ME... ANYMORE.
- ( puffing and panting )
- HAZUKI LEFT BECAUSE OF ME.
IT WAS ALL MY FAULT.
- DON'T SHOULDER THIS ALONE,
HIKARU. WE'RE ALL TO BLAME.
HAZUKI LEFT TO SAVE
THE ENTIRE MIDO CLAN.
- ( sobbing )
- PLEASE COME BACK, MASTER!
MASTER, COME BACK!
- I'M GOING.
WE HAVE TO RESCUE HER.
- HIKARU.
I TOLD YOU, WE PROMISED
WE WOULDN'T TRY TO FOLLOW
HER WHEN SHE LEFT.
I GAVE MY WORD.
- BUT STILL!
- I WOULD FOLLOW HER IF I
THOUGHT IT WOULD DO ANY GOOD.
IT WON'T.
WE DON'T HAVE ANYTHING
TO BEAT THEM WITH.
NOTHING BUT KOUHEI'S JAGAN, AND
HE HASN'T MASTERED IT.
- KOHARU'S WORKING ON THAT.
SHE'S DOING ALL SHE
CAN TO HELP HIM.
BUT SO FAR IT
DOESN'T SEEM TO BE WORKING.
- TELL ME.
WHY DID YOU COME BACK
TO THE CASTLE?
- WELL, IT DEFINITELY WASN'T
BECAUSE I WANTED TO BE HERE.
I HAD TO COME.
I CAME. TO SAVE THE
PEOPLE THAT I LOVE.
BUT I GUESS YOU
WOULDN'T UNDERSTAND.
- NO, I WOULDN'T.
I HATE YOU, LUNA.
- AND THAT'S WHY.
BECAUSE YOU ARE SO LOVED.
YOU'LL NEVER UNDERSTAND.
YOU'RE WAY TOO SPOILED.
DADDY LOVES YOU BEST.
HE ALWAYS HAS.
- REALLY. IF HE
LOVES ME SO MUCH,
WHY'S HE WANT ME LOCKED
UP IN A PLACE LIKE THIS?
I LOVE PEOPLE, SURE.
BUT THEY DON'T LOVE ME BACK.
- KOUHEI LOVES YOU VERY MUCH
AND YOU KNOW IT.
I WANTED HIM TO BE MINE.
BUT OF COURSE YOU HAD TO
MAKE HIM YOUR SLAVE FIRST.
THAT'S HOW IT IS.
YOU GET EVERYTHING I WANT.
AND THAT'S WHY I DECIDED
TO KILL ALL OF THEM.
SINCE I CAN'T KILL YOU, I
THOUGHT THAT COULD ENTERTAIN ME.
I KNEW IF I KILLED KOUHEI
AND YOUR FRIENDS,
IT WOULD MAKE YOU SAD.
I THOUGHT I'D ENJOY THAT.
SOUNDED FUN.
- SHE REMINDS ME...
REMINDS ME OF HOW I USED TO BE.
TRAPPED IN THE CASTLE, ALONE.
I WAS SO MUCH LIKE HER
UNTIL KOUHEI CAME ALONG
AND CHANGED ALL THAT.
I THINK I UNDERSTAND NOW.
YOU'RE ALONE.
I REMEMBER HOW THAT FEELS.
IT'S HARD BEING LONELY.
- I'M NOT LONELY.
I'M NOT ALONE! I HAVE VARGAS.
I'LL ALWAYS HAVE MY FRIEND
RIGHT HERE BESIDE ME.
YOU'RE THE ONE WHO'S
ABOUT TO BE ALONE FOREVER, LUNA.
- IT LOOKS LIKE
THE CASTLE'S DISAPPEARING.
- WHAT'S HAPPENING
TO IT, MASTER?
- THE MAGIC BARRIER IS
PERMANENTLY SEALING,
SO NO ONE WILL BE ABLE TO ENTER.
- PERMANENTLY?
WHY ARE WE JUST STANDING
HERE? DON'T YOU GET IT?
IF WE JUST LET HAZUKI
DISAPPEAR WITH THE CASTLE,
EVERYTHING WE'VE DONE,
EVERYTHING KOUHEI'S DONE,
WAS JUST A BIG WASTE OF TIME!
I'M GOING!
YOU CAN ALL STAY HERE.
- I WANNA HELP TOO.
I'LL COME.
- STAY HERE. KOUHEI NEEDS
YOUR HELP, REMEMBER?
STAY WITH HIM.
HE IS YOUR FIANCEE, RIGHT?
- RIGHT.
- MASTER, I'M COMING! I DON'T
CARE IF I'M BREAKING MY PROMISE!
- PLEASE FORGIVE US ALL, HAZUKI.
- WAIT!
THERE'S SOMETHING ELSE
THE TWO OF US HAVE TO DO.
I SUMMON THE ELEMENTS! FIRE!
WATER! WOOD! METAL! EARTH!
WE HAVE TO KEEP
THE BARRIER OPEN.
AT LEAST UNTIL
KOUHEI'S READY.
- LET'S HOPE HE'S READY SOON.
THIS WON'T LAST MUCH LONGER!
- SO, THE SISTER AND HER
CLOWN ARE STILL HERE.
- ( crashes )
PRINCESS ARTE.
IT'S TIME FOR BIG SIS
TO FINALLY RETURN TO HERSELF.
HOPE YOU ENJOYED
THE SABBATICAL, MISTRESS LUNA.
THIS IS A GROWN-UP TASK,
ASSIGNED ONLY TO ME.
I WANT THE TWO OF YOU TO LEAVE.
- NO.
I'M STAYING.
I WANT TO SEE LUNA CHANGE.
- IF YOU INSIST.
WHO AM I TO ARGUE WITH ROYALTY?
- YOU HAD BETTER
KEEP YOUR PROMISE!
YOU SWORE YOU'D NEVER GO AFTER
THEM AGAIN IF I DID THIS.
KOUHEI OR ANY OF THE REST!
- OF COURSE, MISTRESS.
IF YOU'D COME BACK
WILLINGLY WHEN I ASKED,
WE COULD'VE AVOIDED
THAT LAST LITTLE ROW.
- OH, REALLY? WELL IF
YOU'D JUST LEFT ME ALONE
AND NOT COME AFTER ME, THEN
NONE OF THIS WOULD'VE HAPPENED.
AND I'D BE WITH THEM NOW
INSTEAD OF BACK IN THIS
STUPID CASTLE WITH YOU!
- AND IF YOU HAD STAYED WHERE
YOU BELONGED IN THE FIRST PLACE,
INSTEAD OF RUNNING AWAY WITH
THAT BOY AND MURDERING KINKEL,
I WOULDN'T HAVE
HAD TO CHASE YOU.
BUT I SUPPOSE IT'S ALL WATER
UNDER THE BRIDGE NOW.
- ( he sniggers )
- I CALL YOU, MASTER!
SHOW US YOUR POWER!
- GOOD-BYE, KOUHEI.
TIME TO GO.
- ISN'T THIS GREAT?
HAZUKI'S GOING AWAY.
YOU'LL FINALLY BE FREE.
YOU WON'T HAVE TO BE
AFRAID ANYMORE.
ISN'T THAT GOOD?
- I... I DON'T KNOW.
- ( she screams )
- ARE WE FIGHTING FOR NOTHING?
WITHOUT KOUHEI'S POWER,
IT'S POINTLESS!
- EVEN WITHOUT A FULL MOON,
THIS PENDANT HAS THE POWER TO
TRANSFORM YOU BACK
INTO MISTRESS LUNA.
ANY PHASE OF THE MOON
WILL SUFFICE.
ONCE AROUND YOUR NECK,
YOU'LL NEVER BE ABLE TO
REMOVE IT WITH YOUR OWN HANDS.
YOU'LL BE LUNA FOREVER.
- I KNOW HOW IT WORKS.
EVENTUALLY, I'LL LEARN
NOT TO MIND BEING LUNA AGAIN.
AND MAYBE THEN, WE CAN ACTUALLY
GET ALONG TOGETHER AS FRIENDS.
OR EVEN AS SISTERS, Y'KNOW?
- AS SISTERS?
- YEAH.
BECAUSE THEN,
I'LL BE JUST LIKE YOU.
- THANK YOU, ALL OF YOU,
FOR EVERYTHING.
I'M SO SORRY, KOUHEI.
- Hiraku: HAZUKI!
- Haiji: MASTER! WE'RE HERE!
- HIKARU! HAIJI!
MASTER YAYOI!
- WHAT... WHAT'S GOING ON?
- WELL, WHAT DO YOU THINK?
WE CAME TO RESCUE YOU!
- YOU CAME FOR ME?
- SURE, OF COURSE WE DID!
AND YOU'D BETTER
APPRECIATE IT!
WE'VE PUT UP WITH A LOT JUST
TO GET IN HERE, SUCKER-HEAD!
- I'M SURE YOU DID. BUT THEN
WHAT THE HECK'S THE POINT OF ME
COMING ALL THE WAY BACK HERE
IN THE FIRST PLACE, DORK MAIDEN?
- OH, STOP WHINING,
MONSTER GIRL.
IT'S YOUR OWN FAULT ANYWAY
FOR JUST RUNNING OFF LIKE THAT.
YOU LEFT KOUHEI ALL ALONE.
- I HAD TO.
THE OTHERS MAY HAVE PROMISED NOT
TO FOLLOW YOU, BUT I NEVER DID!
AND BESIDES, YOU
KNOW KOUHEI WOULD
DO THE SAME THING
PROMISE OR NOT!
- LET'S GET GOING.
- OKAY!
- HOW 'BOUT YOU COME WITH US.
- I DON'T THINK SO!
- ( she screams )
- I'M THE KEEPER OF THIS CASTLE
NOW.
AND I WON'T LET ANYONE
TAKE YOU AGAIN.
- LET ME GO, YOU JERK!
THIS WASN'T PART OF THE DEAL!
YOU PROMISED YOU'D LEAVE THEM
ALONE IF I CAME BACK!
THAT'S THE ONLY REASON I DID!
- THEY BROKE THE DEAL FIRST
BY COMING AFTER YOU.
NOW IT'S OPEN SEASON,
AND A PERFECT CHANCE
TO GET RID OF THEM FOR GOOD.
- YOU CAN'T TURN ME INTO
LUNA NOW, THERE'S NO POINT!
KOUHEI. HELP ME. KOUHEI!
- WHY AM I JUST SITTING HERE
DOING NOTHING BUT BEING SCARED?
HELPING HAZUKI WAS THE REASON
I GOT THIS POWER IN
THE FIRST PLACE!
I HAVE TO DO SOMETHING.
AT LEAST TRY TO SAVE HER.
- NOW, KOUHEI.
- NOW. PLEASE, KOUHEI.
- GRANDMOTHER? GRANDMOTHER!
- ( he screams)
- I WANTED TO SHOW YOU
THIS PLACE.
I THOUGHT YOU'D LIKE IT.
- HAZUKI.
HAZUKI!
- DAMN YOU, JEDA!
HAVE YOU FORGOTTEN THE
PRINCESS IS STILL HERE!
- ARE YOU ALL RIGHT, VARGAS?
- PRINCESS, I'M SORRY.
- NO. VARGAS.
- COME WITH US!
RUN. NOW!
- CHILD'S PLAY.
- YEAH, YOU'LL HAVE TO DO
BETTER THAN THAT!
- YOU LUNA, THE DAY WALKER,
ARE ALL THAT MATTERS.
ARTE AND VARGAS WERE
SIDESHOWS JUST LIKE THE REST.
NOW IT'S TIME TO CLEAN HOUSE.
I FIGURED THIS ONE
MIGHT STILL BE USEFUL.
SO I BROUGHT HIM ALONG.
- IT'S SEIJI.
STILL IN A TRANCE.
- HIKARU, LOOK OUT!
- SEIJI! YOU'VE COME BACK!
- LIGHTING STRIKE!
- BROKE FREE OF MY SPELL.
MUST BE STRONGER THAN I THOUGHT.
OH, WELL, THE PUPPETRY
WAS JUST FOR FUN.
I'LL HAVE NO PROBLEM
KILLING THEM ALL MYSELF.
- EVERYONE'S RISKING
THEIR LIVES FOR ME.
BUT I DIDN'T WANT THIS.
NOT AGAIN.
KOUHEI!
- Kouhei: YOU CALLED?
- KOHEI. YOU'RE HERE.
- WHAT? BUT NO, IT'S TOO LATE.
SHE HAS THE NECKLACE NOW.
ANY MOMENT SHE'LL BECOME
MISTRESS LUNA AGAIN.
YOU CAN'T STOP IT, YOU HUMAN
WASTE. IT'S HER DESTINY!
- WELL, THAT'S A DESTINY
I'LL JUST HAVE TO CHANGE.
- ( he yells )
- SO THIS IS JAGAN?
- ( she screams )
- SORRY FOR THE WAIT, HAZ.
- YOU REALLY DID COME.
OH, KOUHEI!
KOUHEI, I THOUGHT
I'D LOST YOU FOR GOOD.
YOU MEAN YOU AREN'T
SCARED ANYMORE?
- WHO, ME?
NAH.
- I'M SO GLAD.
I'M NOT CRYING, OKAY? I'M NOT
CRYING EVEN A LITTLE BIT!
OF COURSE YOU SHOULD'VE COME
SOONER, YOU'RE MY SLAVE.
WHAT TOOK YOU SO LONG ANYHOW,
YOU BIG DOPE?
- I KNOW YOU'RE RIGHT, HAZ.
I SHOULD'VE BEEN HERE FOR YA.
TAKE SOME BLOOD.
WE'LL CALL IT EVEN, OKAY?
- NO! YOU CAN'T!
- IT'S OVER NOW.
- ( he yells )
- HUMAN WASTE!
- ( theme song playing )
- ( singing in Japanese )
- NOW HERE'S A REALLY HARD
RIDDLE FOR YOU, BIG BROTHER!
WHO IS THE MOST IMPORTANT PERSON
IN THE WHOLE WORLD TO ME?
IT TOOK ME A LONG TIME
TO FIGURE THIS OUT,
BUT I THINK I'VE
FINALLY GOT IT.
FULL, FULL, FULL MOON! OH, COME
ON, DON'T MAKE ME SAY IT,
THAT'S JUST MEAN.
A LADY SHOULD NEVER HAVE
TO EXPLAIN HERSELF, OKAY?
SERIOUSLY, DON'T BE SO DENSE!
NEXT TIME ON MOONPHASE:
"THEY SAY IT'S THE END!"
BUT IT'S NOT REALLY, RIGHT?
I MEAN, WON'T YOU
ALWAYS BE MY SLAVE?