- ( water flowing )
- ( rustling )
- ( wind blowing )
- ( whimpering )
- ( Vargas laughs diabolically )
- SO YOU'RE THE ONE WHO
ATTACKED KOUHEI, AREN'T YOU?
ANSWER ME!
WHERE'S KOUHEI NOW?
- ( muffled groaning )
- PUT HER DOWN!
I'M WARNING YOU, YOU BULLY!
- Vargas: THOSE EYES.
THAT MOUTH.
YOU RESEMBLE THE PRINCESS,
JUST AS I EXPECTED.
- ( theme song playing )
( singing in Japanese )
- ( Hikaru groaning )
- (Vargas laughing )
- Vargas: THOSE EYES.
THAT MOUTH.
YOU RESEMBLE THE PRINCESS,
JUST AS I EXPECTED.
- WHAT DO YOU MEAN?
- YOU'LL UNDERSTAND SOON ENOUGH.
- (Hazuki and Hikaru gasping )
- ( Hikaru screaming )
- ( thudding )
- ( both whimpering )
- Hazuki: EWW! GROSS!
GET OFF OF ME!
- Hikaru: GRODY! BLECH!
- Hazuki: "BIG BROTHER, WHERE IS
THIS NURSERY RHYME FROM?"
- ( Hikaru whimpering )
- ( screaming )
THAT'S NO FAIR, MY FIRST KISS
WAS SUPPOSED TO BE WITH SEIJI!
NOT SOME DEMON GIRL LAME-O!
- THEN YOU SHOULDN'T'VE PLANTED
YOUR LIPS ON ME, KLUTZ!
- HE THREW ME! YOU SHOULD'VE
MOVED YOUR BIG BUTT!
- DON'T BLAME ME,
STUCK-UP SHRINE GIRL!
MONSTER-FACE FREAK!
- ( Vargas laughing )
LIKE THE SWEET CHIRPING
OF TWO LITTLE BIRDS.
YOU REALLY ARE ADORABLE.
- OOPS. I FORGOT ABOUT HIM.
- BUT A BIRD ONLY SINGS ITS BEST
WHEN IT FEELS SAFE BEHIND BARS,
PROTECTED FROM THE
DANGERS OF THE WORLD.
YOU'RE COMING WITH ME,
MISTRESS LUNA.
BACK TO THE COMFORT
OF YOUR TRUE MASTER'S CAGE.
- ( Hazuki grunting )
- ( Vargas groaning )
HURRY UP, LET'S GO!
- ( Hazuki and Hikaru panting )
- Hikaru: DID YOU SEE
WHAT YOU DID TO HIM?
DON'T YOU THINK THAT
WAS A LITTLE MUCH?
- Hazuki: I DIDN'T
HAVE A CHOICE!
( thinking ) I CAN'T LET ANYONE
ELSE GET HURT BECAUSE OF ME.
- ( squealing )
- ( groaning )
- ( Hikaru and Hazuki panting )
- YOU WON'T GET AWAY FROM ME!
- ( both screaming )
- ( Vargas grunting )
- ( swishing )
- IMPRISON!
- ( Vargas screaming )
SO, YOU'RE THE ONE WHO'S
BEEN HIDING HER.
( groaning )
- ONE ADVANTAGE TO
BEING A HOMEBODY,
YOU HAVE TIME TO
PERFECT YOUR SPELLS.
- Hazuki: MASTER YAYOI!
- DON'T WORRY. HE WON'T BE
ABLE TO BREAK FREE.
- THAT'S NOT IT!
HIS EYES AREN'T RED!
HE HASN'T BEEN FEEDING!
HE'S NOT THE ONE WHO
DRANK KOUHEI'S BLOOD!
- Yayoi: YOU'RE RIGHT. THEN
KOUHEI'S STILL IN DANGER.
- ( groaning )
- FULL, FULL, FULL, MOON.
( thinking ) THAT'S WEIRD.
ALL THE PAIN JUST STOPPED.
IS SHE DOING THAT?
- FEEL BETTER?
- ( yells )
- ( stammering )
UH, YEAH, IT'S LIKE
I DIDN'T EVEN
FALL OFF A CLIFF!
- I'M GLAD TO HEAR THAT.
- I'M NOT SURE WHY,
BUT, UH...
NEKO MIMI?
- ( clattering )
- I NEED TO BE FED NOW.
CAN I EAT THOSE?
- NO. NOT UNLESS YOU WANT
THE TREES TO START TALKIN'.
( Kouhei laughing nervously )
- ( stomach growling )
- ( thinking ) SHE'S HUNGRY,
BUT WHAT CAN I DO?
I DON'T HAVE MUCH TO OFFER.
( aloud ) HERE.
SORRY. THIS IS ALL I'VE GOT.
- ( munching )
IT'S YUCKY.
- YEAH, WELL...
IT'S GUY FOOD.
MADE IT MYSELF, IT'S DESIGNED
FOR NINJA SURVIVAL, MOSTLY,
SO I COULD TELL THAT A GIRL
WOULDN'T REALLY BE INTO IT.
GUESS SHE REALLY IS HUNGRY.
- ( water flowing )
- ( gasping )
- ( Arte singing )
♪ I FOUND THE NEKO MIMI,
FOUND 'EM IN THE NIGHT ♪
♪ AND WHEN I PUT 'EM ON ME,
SOUNDS OF SUCH DELIGHT ♪
♪ I COULD HEAR THE SECRET ONES,
FAR BEYOND MY SIGHT ♪
- ♪ I HEARD 'EM IN
THE MOUNTAINS, ♪
♪ DANCING IN MOONLIGHT ♪
♪ NEKO MIMI MODE,
FULL, FULL, FULL MOON ♪
THAT'S IT! THAT'S THE REST.
I'M SURPRISED YOU KNOW
THAT OLD NURSERY RHYME.
- I LEARNED IT WHEN
I WAS TAUGHT JAPANESE.
- IS THAT RIGHT?
SO, WHERE'D YOU
COME FROM, EXACTLY?
- I LIKE YOU.
LET'S PLAY.
- ( Haiji groaning )
PASSING OUT WAS THE
BIGGEST MISTAKE OF MY LIFE.
NOW I'VE LOST MY MASTER!
OOH! ISN'T THAT HER SLAVE?
HEY! SLAVE BOY!
- Ryuuhei: LEAVE HIM BE.
- OH! IT'S YOU!
- FACING A VAMPIRE WITH
NO ONE TO HELP HIM.
IT'S A VITAL STEP ON THE
PATH TO HIS AWAKENING.
- CAN WE PLAY?
- HOW CAN YOU STAND HERE
WHEN HE'S IN TROUBLE?
- IF HE CAN'T SURVIVE THIS,
HE'LL BE DEAD SOON ANYWAY.
- SO, ANY PARTICULAR
GAMES YOU LIKE?
- BOUNCY BALL.
- ( Kouhei screaming )
HEY! THIS ISN'T WHAT
I HAD IN MIND!
- ( Vargas laughing )
CAN'T BREAK FREE, YOU SAY?
( grunting )
YOUR MAGIC IS A BOOSTER
TO YOUR PHYSICAL TRAP.
WITHOUT THE TRAP,
THERE'LL BE NOTHING
FOR THE SPELL TO ENHANCE!
- HE JUST GREW MORE ARMS!
- SO IF YOU'VE STRUNG
ME TO A TREE...
- ( crashing )
- OH, NO! HE'S FREE!
- ( Vargas laughing )
WHO'S IN TROUBLE NOW?
- Seiji: LIGHTNING STRIKE!
- ( screaming )
- SEIJI'S HERE!
- RIGHT WHEN WE NEED HIM!
- FINALLY CAUGHT UP WITH YOU.
- YOU'LL REGRET THAT.
( screaming )
- SORRY, THERE'S NO
TIME TO PLAY NICE.
- IS THAT SO? I'LL KEEP THAT
IN MIND FOR MYSELF.
- WHO IS THIS MONSTER?
- I'D SAY YOU'VE
BEEN OUTCLASSED.
( laughing )
- ( distant screaming )
- WHAT THE?
( screaming intensifies )
( thudding )
- OH, HEY.
- THAT SOUNDED LIKE KOUHEI.
- HEY.
- ( Vargas grunting angrily )
( yelling )
- NO! KOUHEI!
- YOU'RE SUPPOSED TO BE SERVING
AS THE PRINCESS' TOY, HUMAN.
- THAT'S SORT OF HOW
I WOUND UP HERE.
( laughing sheepishly )
- Vargas: GO BACK
AND ENTERTAIN HER!
- MAN, NOT AGAIN!
- HUH?
- LOOK, CAN WE
TRY SOMETHING ELSE?
I PLAY A MEAN GAME
OF TIC-TAC-TOE!
( screaming )
- ( Arte singing )
♪ I FOUND THE NEKO MIMI,
FOUND 'EM IN THE NIGHT ♪
♪ AND WHEN I PUT 'EM ON ME,
SOUNDS OF SUCH DELIGHT ♪
- SO SHE'S THE VAMPIRE
WHO ATTACKED KOUHEI.
- ♪ I COULD HEAR THE SECRET
ONES, FAR BEYOND MY SIGHT ♪
♪ I HEARD 'EM IN THE MOUNTAINS,
DANCING IN MOONLIGHT ♪
- THAT GIRL?
- ♪ NEKO MIMI MODE,
FULL, FULL, FULL MOON ♪
- ( Kouhei screaming )
- ( Hikaru and Hazuki gasping)
- Vargas: PRINCESS,
THIS ISN'T SAFE.
I THOUGHT WE AGREED YOU WOULD
LEAVE THE SEARCH TO ME.
- BUT IT'S BORING
JUST WAITING THERE.
DIDN'T YOU LIKE OUR
LITTLE BOUNCY BALL GAME?
- ( laughing nervously )
ASK ME AFTER MY HEART
STOPS EXPLODING.
- DID YOU NOT HAVE
ENOUGH FUN YET?
DO YOU WANNA PLAY SOME MORE?
- ( whimpering )
- I THINK WE SHOULD.
- ALL RIGHT, LITTLE MISS CREEPY,
THAT'S ENOUGH!
- THAT'S ENOUGH OF WHAT?
- DON'T YOU GET IT?
HE'S MY SLAVE!
YOU CAN'T PLAY WITH HIM
WITHOUT MY PERMISSION!
- I SEE. SO WE HAVE FOUND YOU.
- Kouhei: IS IT ME, OR DID
IT JUST GET DARKER?
- Hazuki: NO MORE GAMES.
JUST WHO ARE YOU?
- MY NAME IS ARTEMIS.
BUT YOU CAN CALL ME ARTE.
- ARTE?
- ARTEMIS WAS AN ANCIENT
MOON GODDESS. LIKE LUNA.
THAT'S WHERE DADDY
GOT OUR NAMES.
- Vargas: YES, YOU'RE
HALF SISTERS.
SIRED BY OUR MASTER.
BORN TO DIFFERENT MOTHERS.
- SHE'S MY... LITTLE SISTER?
- THERE'S TWO OF US,
SO WE DON'T NEED YOU.
YOU CAN DIE.
- ( Hazuki screaming )
WHAT WAS THAT THING?
- IT'S A SHADOW DEMON.
THAT'S HER SPECIALTY.
SHE'S A SHADOW MASTER.
- ( gasping )
- KAORU SENSED THE
DANGEROUS VIBRATIONS
ON THAT MOUNTAIN LONG AGO.
YET YOU CONTINUE TO TELL ME
NOT TO LET HER HELP?
- IT'S WHAT MASTER YAYOI
AND YOU-KNOW-WHO DECIDED.
FOR KOUHEI'S AWAKENING TO
TAKE PLACE, HE CANNOT BE HELPED.
THIS IS NO TIME FOR EMPATHY.
- YOU WANT US TO IGNORE
OUR FEELINGS?
- THAT'S RIGHT.
- ( sighs )
- Vargas: PRINCESS, YOU MUST
NOT TAKE HER LIFE.
MY ORDERS WERE TO
FIND MISTRESS LUNA
AND RETURN HER
SAFELY TO OUR MASTER.
- BUT, I DON'T UNDERSTAND.
WHY'S THE SLAVE STILL
PROTECTING HER?
I ALREADY KISSED HIS NECK.
- Vargas: WHAT?
BUT THAT CAN ONLY
MEAN ONE THING.
HE IS THE VAMPIRE'S LOVER!
- THAT'S NOT FAIR.
HE'S MY SLAVE!
- ( Hazuki and
Kouhei screaming )
- Kouhei: COME ON!
- ( explosion )
- ( Kaoru gasping )
- Koharu: OH, KAORU.
DON'T YOU GO WANDERING
OFF NOW, I NEED YOUR HELP.
- YOU DO?
- WE'RE GOING TO COOK
SOME RICE BALLS.
I'M SURE THEY'LL ALL BE VERY
HUNGRY WHEN THEY GET BACK.
- BUT I...
- DON'T WORRY, DEAR.
THEY'RE ALL GOING
TO RETURN HOME SAFELY.
GRANDMA CAN FEEL
IT IN HER BONES.
COME NOW,
THE RICE IS WAITING.
- ( whimpering )
- ( both panting )
- DAMN IT.
- Seiji: (thinking )
THESE VAMPIRES' POWERS
SEEM TO HAVE NO END.
- ( thinking ) ARE WE REALLY
SUPPOSED TO JUST STAND HERE?
AND WATCH KOUHEI SUFFER
LIKE HEARTLESS DEMONS?
- NO! NO!
- HIKARU, WHAT'S WRONG?
- THEY CAN'T.
DON'T LET THEM!
- I OWE YOU FOR TAKING MY EYE.
SO I'LL TAKE YOUR LIFE!
- Seiji: MASTER!
- YOU WORRY ABOUT
PROTECTING HIKARU.
- ( thinking ) IS SHE JUST
SCARED? OR IS IT SOMETHING MORE?
- Arte: I WANT TO PLAY.
PLEASE, FORGET ABOUT LUNA.
PLAY WITH ME INSTEAD.
- OH, JUST GIVE UP!
KOUHEI BELONGS
TO ME, NOT YOU,
AND HE DOES WHATEVER
I WANT HIM TO!
AND I DON'T FEEL
LIKE SHARING HIM
WITH A MEAN LITTLE
GIRL LIKE YOU!
- LUNA'S TOY...
I WAS AFRAID
THIS WOULD HAPPEN.
THE SLAVE'S ACTING LIKE DADDY.
ALL THAT HE CARES ABOUT IS YOU.
WITH LUNA AROUND,
WHY WOULD ANYONE
WANNA PAY ATTENTION TO ME?
I HATE HER.
( shouts ) I HATE LUNA!
- Kouhei: ( thinking ) WE WON'T
BE ABLE TO ESCAPE THIS TIME.
DAMN IT, SHE'S GONNA KILL US
WITH A STUPID SHADOW!
NO! THAT DOESN'T MAKE SENSE!
( grunting )
- ( crackling )
- ( Arte screaming )
- KOUHEI...
- HE REPELLED HER SHADOW.
OR WAIT. HE DESTROYED IT!
- Vargas: PRINCESS!
DON'T MOVE!
I'M COMING TO HELP YOU!
PRINCESS!
- MAN, I WASN'T TRYIN' TO
KNOCK HER UNCONSCIOUS.
- WHAT DID YOU EXPECT?
THAT SHADOW WAS PART OF HER.
DESTROYING IT WAS BOUND
TO HURT HER TOO.
- YEAH, I GUESS SO.
- ( cheerfully ) UM, KOUHEI?
YOUR NECK IS ABOUT
TO BE SORE, ALL RIGHT?
- A MERE HUMAN HURTING
THE PRINCESS. UNFORGIVABLE!
YOU'LL SUFFER FOR THIS!
NO. SHE'S FEEDING!
- AS YOU CAN SEE MY POWERS
JUST GOT A MAJOR BOOST.
SO UNLESS YOU WANNA GET
HURT EVEN WORSE TONIGHT,
TAKE THAT GIRL AND
GET OFF THIS MOUNTAIN!
- ( swishing )
- ( crashing )
- I'LL FIGHT YOU MYSELF.
I'M NOT GONNA WATCH SOMEONE
ELSE GET HURT BECAUSE OF ME.
NEVER, EVER AGAIN!
- HAZUKI...
- DID YOU SEE THAT?
SHE HARNESSED HER TRUE POWER.
MAYBE WE REALLY CAN WIN THIS.
- Jeda: ( whispering ) THEN I'D
BETTER STEP IN.
- BROTHER SEIJI!
( Hikaru moaning )
- WHAT THE?
- HIKARU!
- JEDA, WHERE'VE YOU BEEN?
- COMPLICATIONS, MR. VARGAS.
I MUST SAY I'M DISAPPOINTED
IN YOUR PERFORMANCE
WHILE I'VE BEEN GONE.
- WHO'S THIS GUY? HOW MANY
VAMPIRES ARE OUT HERE?
- LISTEN, BUG-HEAD, YOU GIVE
HIKARU BACK TO ME, RIGHT NOW!
- WILL YOU COME WITH US,
LIKE A GOOD LITTLE GIRL?
- Hazuki: I'M NOT GOING
ANYWHERE WITH YOU!
- WELL, THEN. I'LL HAVE TO
MAKE HER MY HOSTAGE.
- NO YOU WON'T!
- JUST HOW SKILLFUL DO YOU
THINK YOU ARE, MISTRESS?
YOU REALLY THINK YOU CAN STOP
US WITHOUT HURTING HER AS WELL?
- Hazuki: HIKARU, NO...
- Kouhei: YOU COWARDS!
SHE'S JUST A KID!
- Jeda: WE'LL GIVE YOU TIME
TO MULL IT OVER.
WOULDN'T WANT YOU TO HURT
YOUR SOFT LITTLE BRAINS.
MEET US BACK HERE, ON THE
NIGHT OF THE NEXT FULL MOON.
- ( Seiji grunting )
- IF YOU EVER WANT TO SEE
THIS GIRL ALIVE AGAIN.
- WHERE IS SHE?
- Jeda: WELL, I'LL BE WAITING,
MISTRESS LUNA.
SWEET DREAMS, PUPPETS
( laughing )
- DAMN IT!
I STILL WASN'T STRONG ENOUGH.
- Ryuuhei: NO, KOUHEI.
- THEY TOOK HER.
I TRIED...
I TRIED TO FIGHT BACK THIS TIME.
- I KNOW.
- BUT IT DIDN'T MATTER.
IT HAPPENED AGAIN.
SOMEONE'S BEEN HURT.
TAKEN AWAY BECAUSE OF ME.
( thinking ) WHY AM I
SUCH A CURSE?
- ( theme song playing )
( singing in Japanese )
- Hazuki: OKAY, BIG BROTHER,
RIDDLE TIME AGAIN!
USUALLY WHEN YOU BREAK
SOMETHING YOU GET IN TROUBLE.
BUT WHAT CAN YOU BREAK
OVER AND OVER AGAIN,
AND GET PRAISED FOR EVERY TIME?
FULL, FULL, FULL, MOON!
YOU GIVE UP? A RECORD! DUH!
YOU KNOW YOU'RE REALLY NOT
GETTING ANY BETTER AT THESE.
WE'VE BEEN DOING 'EM
FOR A WHILE NOW
AND YOU'D THINK EVENTUALLY
SOMETHING WOULD SINK IN.
I-I MEAN, UM, GOOD TRY!
NEXT TIME ON MOON PHASE,
"I DIDN'T KNOW YOU
WERE LIKE THAT!"
GOODNIGHT, BIG BROTHER!