- Frieze: IT'S BEEN
A LONG TIME, MARIO.
- Mario: IT'S GOOD
TO SEE YOU AGAIN.
- WELL, HERE I AM. SO, SPEAK.
- THE ALL-POWERFUL FORTUNETELLER
NEEDS ME TO TELL
HER WHY I'VE COME.
FASCINATING.
- YOU SEEK MISTRESS LUNA.
- VERY GOOD.
WHERE IS SHE?
- IF YOU'VE COME
LOOKING FOR HER,
THAT MEANS YOU KNOW WHAT BECAME
OF COUNT HEINRICH VON KINKEL.
I'D BE CAREFUL.
WOULDN'T WANT TO SHARE HIS FATE.
- DON'T WORRY
ABOUT ME, FORTUNETELLER.
- NO?
- NO. I'M NOT AS WEAK
AS THE COUNT.
- ( chuckles )
- BOOKS.
GOODBYE, FRIEZE. THANK YOU.
- ( theme song playing )
- ( singing in Japanese )
- ( sneezes )
- MAN, IT'S COLD TODAY.
- WELL, THIS COULD TAKE A WHILE.
( yawns )
( gasps )
OH, RIGHT. SHE'S A DAY WALKER.
I GUESS I HAVE TO
GET USED TO THAT.
- Hazuki: ALMOST TIME.
YOU READY?
- Haiji: READY!
- HEY, WHAT'RE YOU GUYS DOING?
- SHH! BE QUIET.
WE'RE IN THE MIDDLE OF A
BATTLE BETWEEN GOOD AND EVIL.
- Kouhei: GOOD AND EVIL?
WHICH ONE ARE YOU?
SO YOU'RE FIGHTING A BUN?
- HERE IT COMES!
- IT'S A CROW.
- ( cawing )
- NOW!
- I'M ON IT!
- ( screams )
- KICK HIS LITTLE CROW BUTT!
LET HIM HAVE IT!
- ( screams )
- ALRIGHT!
- GEEZ. POOR CROW.
- DON'T BE FOOLED BY THE
FORCES OF EVIL. THEY'RE SNEAKY.
- LIKE THAT?
- ( crow caws )
- WHAT?
HE BROUGHT REINFORCEMENTS!
- HE WHAT?
- ( pounding )
- HAIJI!
- NO! MY POOR, SWEET HAIJI.
- ( crow cawing )
- STUPID!
I HATE THOSE EVIL, THIEVING,
UGLY, HORRIBLE, MEAN CROWS!
- WOMEN.
- YOU SHOULDN'T SCOFF
AT MY MASTER'S PAIN.
THIS IS AN EPIC
TALE OF STOLEN LOVE.
AND THE THWARTED
RETRIBUTION THAT FOLLOWS!
IT BEGINS WITH TWO BEAUTIFUL
NEKOMIMI BUNS FROM FURUFURU-DO,
BOUGHT WITH INNOCENT
HOPE FOR A TASTY SNACK
BY THE SWEET YOUNG
GIRL BEFORE YOU.
SHE AND HER SHIKIGAMI JOURNEYED
TO THE KITCHEN TO MAKE TEA
ONLY TO DISCOVER,
UPON THEIR RETURN,
THAT THE BEAUTIFUL BUNS
WERE BEING PILFERED AWAY!
- ( both yell )
- HEY!
COME BACK HERE, YOU FOUL BEAST!
- Haiji: BUT, ALAS,
HE DID NOT RETURN
AND THE FURUFURU-DO BUN
THAT MASTER SO LOVED WAS
NEVER HEARD FROM AGAIN.
AND SO WE HATCHED
A FEARSOME PLOT.
WE'LL NEVER GIVE UP!
- OH, HAIJI, MY TRUE FRIEND!
YOU'RE THE ONLY ONE
IN THE WORLD WHO UNDERSTANDS ME.
- OKAY. SO YOU'RE AT WAR
WITH SOME EVIL CROWS, HUH?
WELL, THAT'S ABOUT AVERAGE
ON THE WEIRD SCALE
FOR A VAMPIRE GIRL.
- THEY SHALL KNOW PAIN!
OH, YES THEY SHALL, MY FRIEND.
- WHY DON'T WE JUST GO
BACK TO THE STORE?
I'LL BUY YOU SOME MORE BUNS
AND NOBODY HAS TO KNOW PAIN.
- THIS IS BIGGER THAN BUNS!
- OKAY.
- THIS IS ABOUT HONOR!
INTEGRITY! VALOR!
AND TEACHING THOSE STUPID LITTLE
BLACK PIGEONS NOT
TO MESS WITH ME!
- SOUNDS LIKE A NOBLE GOAL, HAZ.
- YOU SHUT UP!
I AM A GREAT PREDATOR
AMONG PREDATORS!
I CAN OUTSMART
A COUPLE OF CROWS.
THIS BOWL OF GOODIES WILL
LURE THEM OUT INTO THE OPEN.
QUICK, HAIJI, YOU GO
HIDE UNDER THE HOUSE!
- RIGHT!
- YOU REALLY THINK
THIS IS GONNA WORK?
THEY'RE NOT JUST GONNA FLY DOWN
AND EAT RIGHT OUTTA YOUR HAND.
- OF COURSE IT'LL WORK.
ALL I HAVE TO DO IS
SUPPRESS MY PRESENCE
AND THEY WON'T EVEN NOTICE ME.
- "SUPPRESS YOUR PRESENCE?"
- THAT'S INCREDIBLE.
SHE'S NOT MOVING AT ALL.
DOESN'T EVEN LOOK
LIKE SHE'S ALIVE.
- KOUHEI! WHAT ARE YOU DOING?
- OH, UH, HA. NOTHING.
- WHAT'S THE POINT OF
SUPPRESSING MY PRESENCE
IF YOU'RE JUST GONNA
STAND AROUND ANNOUNCING IT?
- OH! RIGHT, YEAH, SORRY.
I WAS JUST... NEVER MIND.
- THAT'S HOW SHE LOOKED WHEN
I SAW HER FOR THE FIRST TIME
SITTING UP THERE ON
TOP OF THE CASTLE.
I WISH I COULD CAPTURE
THAT SOMEHOW.
YOU KNOW, THAT JUST MIGHT WORK.
- I'M HOME, GRANDPA.
HUH?
- Elfriede: OH, HELLO,
KOUHEI. WELCOME HOME.
- SO, UH, WHAT'RE YOU DOING?
- WHAT, ARE YOU BLIND,
BOY? I'M DOING SIT-UPS.
- Kouhei: IN THE ENTRYWAY?
- YES, WELL, HE LIKES
THE LEVEL OF THE STAIRS.
- Kouhei: WHATEVER. DO EITHER
OF YOU KNOW WHERE HAZUKI IS?
- Ryuuhei: WHAT DO YOU MEAN?
I THOUGHT THE GIRL WAS WITH YOU.
- Kouhei: SHE ISN'T HERE?
- Ryuuhei: I HAVEN'T SEEN HER.
- Elfriede: AND I CAN'T FEEL
HER PRESENCE.
MAYBE SHE WENT OUT
FOR A WHILE.
- NO WAY!
- WHAT'S THE MATTER?
- ( bone cracks )
- Elfriede: OH, DEAR.
- THERE'S NO WAY!
THERE'S NO WAY SHE
COULD HAVE BEEN
SITTING THERE THE
WHOLE TIME I WAS GONE!
THAT WAS LIKE, AN HOUR!
- ( crows cawing )
- I GOTCHA!
- Hazuki: HAIJI! THE ROPE!
- GOT IT!
- Both: YEAH!
BONSAI! BONSAI!
BONSAI! BONSAI! BONSAI!
- Kouhei: Hmm.
- BLESS YOU.
- ( laughs )
- THAT WASN'T A SNEEZE!
- WELL, EXCUSE ME!
IT SOUNDED LIKE A SNEEZE!
- I GOTTA HAND IT TO YOU TWO.
YOU CERTAINLY VANQUISHED
THE BEASTS!
( laughs hysterically )
REALLY. WAY TO GO!
- QUIT LAUGHING AT ME!
- Kouhei: I CAN'T WAIT TO
SEE YOUR NEXT BIG BATTLE!
- WELL, YOU JUST WON YOURSELF
A FRONT ROW SEAT, MISTER!
HAIJI! TIE THAT JERK UP!
- Kouhei: HEY! NO, WAIT!
I WAS JUST KIDDING!
- HAIJI! CUT IT OUT!
- Hazuki: WHO'S LAUGHING NOW,
- I WASN'T LAUGHING
- SIR LAUGHS-A-LOT?
- Kouhei: AT YOU, I SWEAR!
- OUCH! LET ME GO!
- Hazuki: I'M SO FUNNY.
TIGHTER, HAIJI!
- Ryuuhei: WELL, THAT SETTLES
IT. I'M THROUGH WITH SIT-UPS.
- Elfriede: HOW'S YOUR BACK?
IS IT FEELING ANY BETTER YET?
- IT'S BEEN BETTER
BUT I THINK I'LL SURVIVE.
JUST NEED TO LEARN NOT TO
PUSH MYSELF SO HARD.
- YOU KNOW, RYUUHEI,
TRUE ART ONLY BECOMES
MORE VALUABLE AS IT AGES.
THIS VASE WAS PROBABLY
WORTH VERY LITTLE
WHEN IT WAS MADE
ALL THOSE YEARS AGO.
AND NOW IT'S WORTH THOUSANDS,
VALUED MORE FOR THE
HISTORY IT HOLDS
THAN THE CLAY IT WAS MADE WITH.
SOMETIMES THE ONES
THAT SHOW THEIR AGE ARE
MORE VALUABLE
THAN THE ONES THAT DON'T.
SORRY. SILLY TO
GET ALL SENTIMENTAL
OVER A VASE LIKE THAT.
- WELL, YOU GO RIGHT AHEAD.
I IMAGINE YOU'VE LIVED ENOUGH
OF YOUR LIFE WITHOUT SENTIMENT,
SO DON'T BOTHER HOLDING BACK
ON MY ACCOUNT.
AND IF BY CHANCE
YOU GET THE URGE
TO TALK ABOUT SOMETHING
OTHER THAN ART,
I KNOW ONE OLD VASE WHO'S
ALWAYS WILLING TO LISTEN.
- YOU DO, HUH?
WELL, I JUST MIGHT TAKE
YOU UP ON THAT SOMEDAY.
- LET'S JUST TELL THEM
WE'RE CLOSED.
- HELLO! CAN WE HELP YOU?
- I HOPE SO.
- Ryuuhei: HIROMI! HELLO.
- Hazuki: REMEMBER,
YOU PROMISED.
NO GOING BACK ON YOUR WORD.
- I KNOW. A WEEK'S WORTH OF
NEKO-MIMI BUNS FROM FURUFURU-DO.
I GOT IT. DON'T YOU WORRY
YOUR PRETTY LITTLE HEAD.
- A WEEK'S WORTH?
THAT'S INTERESTING.
I THOUGHT WE SAID TEN DAYS.
- ( chuckles )
- FIND YOURSELF
ANOTHER MODEL. I QUIT.
- ALRIGHT, ALRIGHT!
TEN DAYS' WORTH. I PROMISE.
GEEZ. WHAT WERE YOU GONNA
DO, JUMP OUT THE WINDOW?
LOOKS LIKE YOU GOT
YOURSELF A MODEL AGAIN, CUTIE.
- ( sighs )
- Kouhei: THE THINGS
I DO FOR MY ART.
- WAIT! KOUHEI LEFT?
WHERE DID HE GO?
- WELL. I'M NOT SURE EXACTLY.
HE JUST SAID HE WAS TAKING
HAZUKI FOR A LITTLE DRIVE.
- HE WENT FOR A DRIVE?
( grunts ) HE WAS SUPPOSED TO
DO THE OCCULT SHOOT!
- AND I TAKE IT THE DEADLINE
WAS SUPPOSED TO BE TODAY.
- YES! CAN'T THAT DUNCE
REMEMBER ANYTHING?
- YEAH. THIS'LL WORK.
- SO, HOW DO YOU WANT
ME TO POSE, ANYWAY?
LIKE THIS? HUH? WANT
ME TO BLOW YOU A KISS?
- NO.
- WANT ME TO WEAR THESE?
- DEFINITELY NOT.
- YOU'RE STIFLING MY
CREATIVE GENIUS, HERE.
- JUST BE YOURSELF.
I WANNA CAPTURE YOU THE
WAY YOU REALLY ARE, HAZ.
WHAT? WHAT ARE YOU GETTING
ALL EMBARRASSED ABOUT?
- OH, IT'S JUST...
AH! IT'S JUST SO
HOT HERE. THAT'S ALL.
- HOT, HUH?
IN THE MIDDLE OF WINTER.
- ( sneezes )
- SHOULDN'T YOU BE TAKING
PICTURES OR SOMETHING?
WHAT KIND OF PROFESSIONAL
PHOTOGRAPHER ARE YOU, ANYWAY?
- WELL, WE'VE STILL
GOT A FEW HOURS.
- HUH? TILL WHEN?
- I HAVE AN IDEA.
BUT WE HAVE TO WAIT
UNTIL SUNSET.
- Hazuki: SUNSET?
- NICE AND SHINY.
- YEAH.
BUT SINCE WE HAVE
A LITTLE WHILE,
I THOUGHT YOU MIGHT
WANNA DO SOME FISHING.
YOU KNOW, SOMETHING
A LITTLE DIFFERENT.
HAVE YOU EVER DONE THIS BEFORE?
- OF COURSE I HAVE.
I'M LIKE, THE BEST FISHER EVER.
- IS THAT SO? WELL, DIVE IN.
- THANK YOU. JUST WATCH.
I'LL CATCH WAY MORE THAN YOU.
- Haiji: WORMS. BLECH!
- YOU OKAY?
- NO, THANKS!
I DON'T NEED THESE.
- DON'T NEED 'EM?
YOU CAN'T FISH WITHOUT BAIT.
WHAT ARE YOU, NUTS?
- IT'S ALL ABOUT SPIRIT
AND DETERMINATION.
- SO THAT'S A YES, THEN?
- WATCH OUT FISHIES!
- THAT'S RIGHT!
'CAUSE HERE COMES THE MASTER.
- HOW ABOUT I BAIT YOUR
LINE FOR YOU, HAZUKI?
WOULD THAT CHANGE YOUR MIND
ABOUT THESE FAITH-BASED
FISHING METHODS? HUH?
- WELL, IF YOU REALLY
WANNA PUT BAIT ON MY LINE,
I GUESS I CAN'T
STOP YOU. HERE.
- GEE, THAT'S REAL
SWELL OF YOU, HAZ.
I'M GUESSING A
LITTLE THANK YOU
WOULD BE TOO MUCH FOR
ME TO ASK FOR, RIGHT?
- COME ON, HURRY
IT UP, BAIT BOY.
- YEAH, YEAH.
- UH-OH, KOUHEI,
MY WORM ESCAPED.
GUESS I NEED ANOTHER ONE.
- GUESS SO.
- KOUHEI! IT GOT AWAY AGAIN!
- WELL, GUESS IT'S ABOUT
TIME TO TAKE THOSE PICTURES.
- WE CAN'T GO. NOT UNTIL
I CATCH AT LEAST ONE FISH.
( gasps )
KOUHEI! A BITE!
- WHAT? WELL, REEL IN! PULL!
- ( screams )
I CAUGHT A FISH!
- ( chuckles ) THAT'S GREAT!
NOW, GRAB IT!
- EW. NO WAY! I CAN'T!
- SURE YOU CAN!
IT'S GONNA GET AWAY.
- NO, NO, NO.
- Kouhei: COME ON, FISH MASTER!
- Hazuki: I DON'T WANT TO.
PLEASE,KOUHEI, YOU TAKE IT.
TAKE IT! TAKE IT! TAKE IT!
- Haiji: HE TOOK IT!
- Hazuki: THAT'S NOT WHAT
I MEANT! TAKE THE STUPID FISH!
- ( camera clicks )
- WELL, I'D SAY OUR
PHOTO SHOOT WAS A SUCCESS.
WE GOT A LOT OF GOOD STU...
SO DEFENSELESS.
- ( Kouhei yells )
HEY, WHAT THE HECK
WAS THAT FOR, ROMI?
- WHAT WAS THAT FOR?
THAT WAS FOR MISSING THE
OCCULT PHOTO SHOOT, YOU ASS!
- AH.
- "AH"?
THAT'S ALL YOU
HAVE TO SAY IS "AH"?
I HAD TO DO THE
STUPID THING BY MYSELF!
I'M EXHAUSTED.
WOW.
- YEAH, THAT ONE'S NOT
TOO TERRIBLE, IS IT?
- THERE'S SOMETHING ABOUT IT.
I DON'T KNOW WHAT IT IS.
IT'S LIKE HAZUKI'S
GLOWING OR SOMETHING.
- I KNOW. I KEEP TRYING
TO FIGURE IT OUT.
I MEAN, IT'S LIKE SHE JUST...
JUST DRAWS YOU IN.
HEY, WAIT, WHERE'RE YOU
GOING WITH THAT PICTURE?
I NEED THAT BACK!
- I'M JUST BORROWING IT.
- WELL, DON'T LOSE IT.
- DON'T BE STUPID.
- IT'S TIME FOR YOUR INJECTION.
- ( camera clicks )
- OH, LOOK AT HER!
SHE'S JUST SO CUTE!
- OKAY, NEXT COSTUME!
HI!
HEY!
KONICHIWA!
ALLO!
BONJOUR!
ROWR.
- OH, I CAN HARDLY STAND IT!
YOU MUST BE THE CUTEST
LITTLE THING THAT EVER LIVED!
- ( giggles )
MORE! TAKE MORE PICTURES OF
HER, WE'LL NEVER HAVE ENOUGH.
- ALRIGHT. BUT WHERE DID
THIS SUDDEN INTEREST
IN HAVING YOUR PICTURE
TAKEN COME FROM?
- I GUESS I JUST REALIZED
HOW SPECIAL IT MADE ME FEEL.
( metallic thudding )
- SO I'M NOT
IMAGINING IT, CHIEF?
WHAT IS IT ABOUT IT?
- Chief Editor: I DON'T KNOW
IT'S CERTAINLY COMPELLING.
FOR ONE THING, IT'S TOO
GOOD TO BE A COMPOSITE,
NOT THAT MORIOKA WOULD DO THAT.
BUT IT MEANS IT
HASN'T BEEN TOUCHED UP,
WHICH WOULD SEEM IMPOSSIBLE.
- IT WAS CLEARLY TAKEN AT NIGHT,
BUT IT'S A GREATER
DEPTH OF FIELD
WHICH MEANS A HIGHER F-STOP.
SO THE SHUTTER WAS
OPEN LONG ENOUGH TO LET
QUITE A BIT OF LIGHT
THROUGH THE SMALL APERTURE.
I MEAN, THAT'S THE ONLY WAY
HE COULD'VE GOTTEN THIS EFFECT.
- OKAY. TOO MUCH SHOP TALK.
- IN OTHER WORDS, THAT GIRL
HAD TO STAND IN THAT POSITION,
COMPLETELY STILL, LONG ENOUGH
FOR THE STARS TO
SHIFT BEHIND HER.
- Hiromi: BUT...
THAT'S IMPOSSIBLE!
- Hazuki: ELFRIEDE,
CAN I ASK YOU SOMETHING?
- OF COURSE.
- HOW COME YOU...
GIVE IN TO MY WHIMS ALL
THE TIME THE WAY YOU DO?
- WELL, I GUESS IT'S
BECAUSE I UNDERSTAND IT.
THE NEED TO
TEST YOUR FREEDOM.
- TEST MY FREEDOM?
- TO EXPERIENCE ALL YOU CAN,
NOW THAT YOU'RE FINALLY
RELEASED FROM YOUR PRISON,
IT'S THE SAME FOR ME.
- THE SAME FOR YOU.
BUT NOT FOR THEM.
WHEN KOUHEI WAS
TAKING MY PICTURE TODAY,
MY REASONS FOR LETTING
HIM WERE SIMPLE.
I WANTED HIM TO. IT WAS FUN.
I LIKE SPENDING TIME WITH HIM.
IT ISN'T THE SAME FOR HIM.
IT ISN'T THE SAME
FOR ANY OF THEM, ACTUALLY.
THEY'RE KIND ENOUGH TO LET
ME STAY HERE WITH THEM.
BUT WHEN THEY LOOK AT
ME THEY SEE AN ORPHAN,
SOMEBODY TO BE PITIED, AND
TREATED LIKE SHE BELONGS.
I HATE SEEING THEM
LOOK AT ME LIKE THAT.
- ( laughing )
AND THAT'S WHAT YOU THINK
YOU SEE WHEN THEY LOOK AT YOU?
- YOU'RE LAUGHING AT ME?
THAT'S JUST CRUEL.
- I'M SORRY. I DO LOVE
YOU, HAZUKI, VERY MUCH.
OKAY?
- HEY! WHOA! I DIDN'T KNOW
THAT YOU WERE INTO GIRLS!
LISTEN, MAYBE WE
SHOULDN'T BATHE TOGETHER.
- ( laughs )
- Hazuki: GET OUT OF
MY BATH, YOU PERVERT!
- Elfriede: HAZUKI, PLEASE!
- Hazuki: NO WAY.
I DON'T CARE HOW
MUCH YOU BEG ME!
- Kouhei: WHAT CAN
I DO TO HELP HER?
- ( theme song playing )
- ( singing in Japanese )
- Hazuki: OH, BIG BROTHER!
YOU DON'T HAVE TO BEG ME
TO DO RIDDLES WITH YOU!
I'VE BEEN SAVING ONE
UP JUST FOR YOU! READY?
IF YESTERDAY HAD BEEN
WEDNESDAY'S TOMORROW,
AND TOMORROW IS
SUNDAY'S YESTERDAY,
WHAT DAY WOULD TODAY BE?
FULL, FULL, FULL... MOON!
NEXT TIME ON MOON
PHASE, EPISODE 17,
"BIG BROTHER, WHY IS
THIS HAPPENING?"
READY FOR THE ANSWER?
IT'S FRIDAY! I THINK.
WHAT WAS THE QUESTION?