MY BIG BROTHER.
NOW, BIG BROTHER,
YOU BELONG TO ME.
- ( theme song playing )
- ( singing in Japanese )
- ( gasps )
WHAT'S GOING ON?
WHAT JUST HAPPENED TO ME?
- YOU MAY CALL ME LUNA.
THIS IS THE FIRST TIME
THAT I'VE TASTED HUMAN BLOOD.
NOW, PLACE YOUR LIPS ON MY HAND.
PROVE YOUR LOYALTY TO ME.
- YEAH, THAT'S IT. RIGHT THERE.
THAT'S THE LOOK I
WANTED TO CAPTURE.
WHATEVER YOU DO, DON'T MOVE.
- ( gasps )
- WHERE DID I PUT MY CAMERA?
MAN, I HOPE I DIDN'T
LOSE IT AGAIN.
- ( chuckles ) RIGHT.
LET'S SEE THAT LOOK.
- ( grunts )
- UH, THAT'S NOT QUITE
WHAT I WAS LOOKING FOR.
IT WAS SOMETHING WITH A LITTLE
MORE PRIDE BEHIND THE EYES.
YOU THINK YOU COULD TRY
TO GET THAT BACK FOR ME?
HAZUKI?
- ( gasps )
- ( screaming )
- WHAT THE HELL?
OKAY, HAZUKI, LET ME GO!
- NEVER CALL ME
BY MY NAME AGAIN.
YOU WILL ADDRESS ME AS
"MISTRESS" OR "GODDESS"
AND NOTHING ELSE. GOT IT?
- HAZUKI, LET ME GO.
- HMM.
- THAT HURT, MAN.
OW, MY FACE.
- COME HERE
AND SMASH THIS THING.
THEN I'LL FINALLY BE FREE
FROM THIS PLACE!
- OKAY.
- OW.
- I GAVE YOU AN ORDER.
- ( growls )
- HEY, WHAT'S THE
MATTER WITH YOU?
WHAT IS WITH THIS HIGH
AND MIGHTY ROUTINE?
- OH, I'M SORRY.
PLEASE DON'T CRY.
- ( screams )
- YOU'RE STILL THE SAME.
- HUH?
- YOU HAVEN'T CHANGED AT ALL.
WHY? WHY HAVEN'T YOU CHANGED?
STUPID! STUPID! STUPID!
STUPID! STUPID!
- WHAT DID YOU EXPECT ME
TO CHANGE INTO? A FLYING COW?
I'M NOT A MAGICIAN.
I'M JUST A REGULAR GUY.
- YOU SHOULD BE MY SLAVE.
- YOUR SLAVE?
WHAT, ARE YOU CRAZY?
- NO, I'M NOT CRAZY.
IT'S SUPPOSED TO HAPPEN
WHEN I KISS SOMEONE.
YOU BECOME MY SLAVE
FOR THE REST OF ETERNITY.
- WELL, I HATE TO TELL YOU THIS,
BUT I'M NOT ANYONE'S SLAVE,
NO MATTER WHO I'M KISSING.
ESPECIALLY IF IT'S
A KISS FROM YOU.
- OH, YEAH? YOU THINK YOU CAN
LOOK ME IN THE EYES
AND SAY THAT?
- UH-HUH.
- HOW ABOUT NOW?
- NOW? WHAT ABOUT NOW?
- I MEAN, HOW DO YOU FEEL ABOUT
DOING EVERYTHING I SAY NOW?
- NO FREAKING WAY.
- ( screams )
- YOU'RE NOTHING BUT
A BIG, MEAN, STUPID-HEAD!
YOU MAKE ME CRAZY!
- ( sighs )
- I HATE YOU, I HATE YOU,
I HATE YOU!
AFTER ALL MY PRACTICE...
I WAITED SO LONG AND I TRIED
SO HARD AND FOR ALL MY TROUBLE,
ALL I GOT WAS EMBARRASSED.
AND YOU'RE EXACTLY THE SAME.
WHY WON'T YOU CHANGE?
YOU DON'T KNOW
HOW AWFUL THIS IS!
I'M STUCK IN THIS
HORRIBLE CASTLE
UNTIL YOU START
OBEYING MY ORDERS.
- ( thunder rumbling )
- HERE AT THE SCHWARTZ QUELLE
CASTLE IN SOUTHERN GERMANY,
STRANGE HAPPENINGS ARE
CHURNING INSIDE IT'S WALLS.
WHAT ENERGIES WIND
THEIR WAY THROUGH
THESE OLD STONE HALLWAYS
MARRED BY TRAGEDY?
THE RENOWNED PSYCHIC SEIJI MIDO
AND HIS CAMERAMAN KOUHEI MORIOKA
HAVE BOTH ENTERED THE CASTLE,
COURAGEOUS TO FACE
WHAT EVILS MAY LURK.
THE QUESTION THAT REMAINS IS,
WILL THEY RETURN UNHARMED?
( sighs )
I HOPE YOU TWO ARE ALL RIGHT.
I DON'T WANNA LEAVE HERE ALONE.
- ( thunderbolt )
- Vigo: HOW PATHETIC.
TOSSING AROUND SUCH
UNINSPIRED PSYCHIC ATTACKS
WITH NO SPIRITUAL ABILITY.
NOW ALL THAT REMAINS IS TO RID
THIS PLACE OF THAT OTHER ONE.
THE ONE WHO CROSSES
MY MASTER'S BARRIER
WITH NO REGARD
FOR HIS SPIRITUAL DEFENSES.
- Seiji: YES. MY COUSIN'S
ALWAYS BEEN A BIT THICK-HEADED.
- HUH?
- SORRY, I'D RATHER NOT HAVE
HAD TO PLAY DEAD FOR YOU.
UNFORTUNATELY,
IT WAS THE ONLY WAY
I COULD THINK OF TO GET YOU
OUTSIDE OF THAT BARRIER.
- I, SEE. SO, YOU, UNLIKE YOUR
FRIEND, CAN SEE ALL THIS!
- ( thunder rumbling )
- THEN YOU'RE NO ORDINARY HUMAN.
- THAT MAKES US EVEN, MY FRIEND.
I CALL ON AMEI,
GOD OF THE EAST SEA.
SHUKURYOU, GOD OF THE WEST SEA.
KYOJOU, GOD OF THE SOUTH SEA.
KUGYOU, GOD OF THE NORTH SEA.
GODS OF THE FOUR SEAS,
GUARDIANS OF US ALL.
DISPERSE THIS EVIL.
KYUU KYUUNYO RITSURYO!
- ( screams )
- SO THERE'S A BARRIER
OF PSYCHIC ENERGY
SURROUNDING THIS CASTLE.
- YES. AND ONLY
WHEN IT'S BROKEN CAN I LEAVE.
SO YOU BELIEVE ME?
- OF COURSE. MY GRANDPA NEVER
STOPS TALKING ABOUT THIS STUFF.
I'VE BEEN AROUND IT
MY WHOLE LIFE.
- I CAN'T EVEN TOUCH IT,
THE BARRIER. I'M TRAPPED.
I CAN'T TOUCH IT
OR THE PERSON WHO CREATED IT.
THAT'S WHY, I NEEDED YOU.
- ( sighs )
WELL...
- IF I COULD SHATTER THAT THING
MYSELF, I WOULD'VE DONE IT.
- SURE, WHY NOT?
IT'S JUST A CRYSTAL.
SHOULDN'T BE HARD TO BREAK
IF I PUT MY BACK INTO IT.
- ( gasps )
- THERE'S JUST ONE LITTLE THING
YOU NEED TO DO FOR ME FIRST,
THEN I'LL SMASH THAT
SUCKER, NO SWEAT.
SOUNDS LIKE A PLAN, SHORTY?
- HMM. WHAT DO YOU WANT?
- I JUST WANT YOU TO SAY
SOMETHING, YOU KNOW, LIKE,
"BIG BROTHER, BREAK THAT
CRYSTAL, PRETTY PLEASE!"
- HUH? PRETTY PLEASE?
YOU WANT ME TO SAY
"PRETTY PLEASE" TO MY SLAVE?
- ( sigh ) YOU KNOW,
YOU'RE PRACTICALLY BEGGING
FOR A GOOD PUNCH IN THE MOUTH.
- A GOOD SLAVE WOULDN'T TALK
TO HIS MASTER THAT WAY!
- YEAH? WELL YOU'RE NOT
MY MASTER, YOU SCHIZO!
FIRST YOU'RE ALL LOVEY,
THEN YOU TURN PSYCHO.
I MEAN, WHAT THE HELL
IS THE MATTER WITH YOU?
- ( inaudible )
- I SAY CHOOSE A PERSONALITY
AND STICK WITH IT.
- I'M A GIRL! MOOD SWINGS
COME WITH THE TERRITORY,
DON'T YOU KNOW THAT?
- I GUESS I'M LEARNING.
- ( rumbling )
- WHOA. WHAT'S WITH
THAT RUMBLING?
- OH, NO. THIS ISN'T GOOD.
HE'S COMING BACK!
- ( both screaming )
- ( groaning )
- Vigo: UNFORGIVABLE!
YOU DARE ENTER THE CASTLE
I AM CHARGED WITH PROTECTING
AND TRY TO LURE AWAY
MY MISTRESS?
- UH, IF THE GIANT TALKING HEAD
IS REAL,
THEN IT'S TIME FOR
ME TO GO HOME.
- I DON'T THINK I'VE EVER SEEN
VIGO THIS UPSET BEFORE.
HE'S ACTUALLY BECOME
THE CASTLE WALLS.
- AH!
- YOU THINK YOU CAN RUN
FROM ME?
- ( screams )
- ( Vigo growling )
- ( both panting )
- WE HAVE TO THINK
OF ANOTHER PLAN.
IT DOESN'T SEEM LIKE
SMASHING THAT CRYSTAL
IS GONNA BE SUCH AN EASY TASK.
- YEAH, YA THINK?
WELL, FORGET IT!
I'VE HAD JUST ABOUT
ENOUGH OF THIS CRAZY FARM.
I'M OUT OF HERE!
- IT'S REALLY NOT THAT BAD.
- OH, NO?
- JUST CALM DOWN. THERE'S
NO WAY VIGO CAN HURT ME.
YOU'LL BE SAFE AND SOUND
AS LONG AS YOU STICK BY MY SIDE.
LET ME FILL YOU IN
ON A LITTLE SECRET.
DESTROY THE CRYSTAL I SHOWED YOU
AND YOU DESTROY THE
SOURCE OF VIGO'S POWER.
SO, WHAT'S IT GONNA BE, HUH?
- I GUESS I DON'T HAVE A CHOICE.
I'LL FIND THE STUPID CRYSTAL.
- THANK YOU.
COME ON NOW, LET'S HUG!
- ( sighs )
- ( chuckles )
- HEY, GET OFF!
- I MAY NOT KNOW MUCH
ABOUT THE SPIRIT WORLD,
BUT EVEN I CAN FEEL THAT ENERGY.
- WE'RE SO FAR APART AND
HE CAN STILL COUNTER EVERY
SPELL I THROW HIS WAY.
AMAZING!
- I HAVE BEEN
ENTRUSTED BY MY MASTER
TO MAKE SURE NO ONE PENETRATES
THIS CASTLE.
NO MATTER HOW GREAT
THEIR ENERGY.
- ( Kouhei panting )
( gasps )
A DEAD END.
- AWAY WITH YOU.
YOU CAN PUT ME DOWN NOW
IF YOU WANT TO.
- OH. SURE.
- FOLLOW ME.
- ( screaming )
- HAZUKI, NO!
- Vigo: I CANNOT ALLOW YOU
TO LEAVE, MISTRESS LUNA.
- PUT ME DOWN RIGHT NOW, VIGO!
- THAT WOULD BE A VIOLATION
OF MY SWORN OATH
AND I CANNOT DO THAT.
- KOUHEI, GET TO THE CRYSTAL!
- BUT, BUT I DON'T EVEN KNOW
WHAT I'M SUPPOSED TO DO WITH IT.
- KNOCK IT TO THE FLOOR
AND SHATTER IT.
FREE ME.
- I'LL GET YOU OUT OF HERE.
I GOTTA BE A MORON PUTTING
MYSELF THROUGH ALL THIS TROUBLE!
- NO, THIS CANNOT BE!
HE'S IMMUNE TO MY ATTACKS!
EVERY OUNCE OF ENERGY THAT
I USE AGAINST HIM IS WASTED!
- AH, GEEZ. WHAT IS THAT?
( gasps )
( screams )
( grunts )
OH, NO.
- ( Vigo screaming )
- WHAT'S HAPPENING?
- IT'S THE AMULET
THAT GRAMPS GAVE ME.
I GET IT.
THIS PROTECTED ME.
- I'LL SEE YOU DEAD FOR THIS!
- ( screams )
- I SEE YOUR INJURY
IS NO RUSE THIS TIME.
WHICH MEANS MY NEXT MOVE
WILL SEAL YOUR FATE.
- PUT ME DOWN. IT'S OKAY.
GO AHEAD.
YOU CAN GET RID OF HIM.
HE DISHONORED THE BLOOD PACT
WHEN HE REFUSED TO BECOME
MY SLAVE. UNFORGIVABLE.
- ( panting )
NO TIME LIKE THE PRESENT.
HERE GOES.
- ( rumbling )
- HUH?
( screams )
- YOUR DAY OF RECKONING
HAS COME. PREPARE TO DIE!
- ( screams )
I BET I CAN HIT THAT
THING FROM HERE.
( grunts )
- IS THAT...
AN INCARNATION?
- ( screaming ) NO!
- NO!
- HAZUKI, GET OUTTA HERE!
- WE DON'T WANT YOU HURT,
MISTRESS LUNA. YOU SHOULD LEAVE.
- I DON'T KNOW WHAT
YOU'RE THINKING,
BUT MY NAME IS NOT LUNA!
I'M NO ONE'S CAGED BIRD.
AND I REFUSE TO STAY IN THIS
HORRIBLE CASTLE ANY LONGER!
- THAT'S IT.
THERE IS IT'S WEAKNESS!
- ( screams )
- ( roars )
- HUH?
- YOU AND ME, YOU PIECE OF JUNK.
YOU'VE STOLEN ENOUGH
OF HAZUKI'S LIFE!
- ( screams )
- ( screaming )
- NOW, THAT'S SOMETHING
YOU DON'T SEE EVERY DAY.
- IT'S TIME TO SAY
GOODBYE, LUNA.
YOU COULD ONLY EXIST
INSIDE THE BARRIER
AND NOW IT'S GONE FOREVER.
YOU'RE NO LONGER PART OF ME.
- HAZUKI, WHERE ARE WE?
( screams ) HAZUKI!
- ( theme song playing )
- ( singing in French )
- Hiromi: IT'S TIME TO
GO HOME, KOUHEI.
WE SEARCHED THIS
WHOLE PLACE FOR HER.
SHE'S NOT HERE ANYMORE.
- Seiji: I DON'T SENSE
ANY HUMANS OR SPIRITS
ANYWHERE IN THE AREA.
I THINK THIS PLACE IS EMPTY.
- Hiromi: WELL, AN EMPTY CASTLE
REALLY PUTS OUR STORY
IN THE TOILET.
"THE CASE FILE
OF PSYCHIC SEIJI MIDO."
"A SPECIAL EDITION, SPIRITS IN A
GERMAN CASTLE" BY HIROMI ANZAI.
UGH, IT SOUNDED SO GOOD.
I GUESS IN THE END,
SHE WAS PROBABLY
JUST YOUR AVERAGE
GHOST ANYWAY.
BUT, HEY, YOU SHOULD BE GLAD
YOU FINALLY GOT TO SEE ONE.
YOU'VE GRADUATED FROM
BEING IMPERVIOUS TO SPIRITS
TO SENSING THEM...
A BIT. PRETTY COOL.
- Kouhei: BUT WOULD A GHOST
HAVE PHYSICAL SHAPE?
WOULD IT ACTUALLY FEEL WARM?
DO GHOSTS KISS?
- ( airplane engine whirring )
- IT FIGURES THE STUPID AIRLINE
WOULD LOSE MY LUGGAGE.
I HAD ALL MY GOOD LENSES
PACKED IN THERE.
IF THEY DON'T FIND MY STUFF,
I'M OUT HUNDREDS.
MAN, THIS TOTALLY SUCKS.
( sighs )
HI, GUYS. I'M HOME.
- GOOD. KOUHEI, IT'S ABOUT TIME.
COME ON IN.
- THEY NEVER FOUND YOUR LUGGAGE,
HUH? THAT'S TOO BAD.
- AT LEAST YOU MADE
IT HOME SAFE.
- GEEZ, WE'VE BEEN
WAITING FOREVER.
WHAT TOOK YOU SO
LONG, BIG BROTHER?
- I GOT STUCK IN CUSTOMS.
IT SUCKED!
( gasps )
( exclaiming in fright )
- OH, RIGHT, I THINK
I OWE YOU AN APOLOGY
FOR SAYING HAZUKI WAS A GHOST,
'CAUSE UH, SHE'S, SHE'S NOT.
- SHE EXPLAINED
THE SITUATION TO US.
IT SEEMS YOU TWO HAD YOURSELVES
QUITE AN ADVENTURE IN
THAT DARK CASTLE.
- YOU'RE TELLING ME THIS DOESN'T
SEEM A LITTLE UNUSUAL
TO YOU GUYS?
I MEAN WHAT THE HECK
IS SHE DOING IN MY HOUSE?
- ACTUALLY, THIS IS MY HOUSE.
I JUST LET YOU LIVE
HERE RENT FREE.
- OH, CUT IT OUT GRANDPA.
MAYBE YOU WANNA
EXPLAIN THIS TO ME.
- I JUST WANTED TO SEE YOU
AGAIN. WHAT'S WRONG WITH THAT?
DO YOU MISS ME, BIG BROTHER?
- ( sighs ) JUST TELL ME
WHAT YOU'RE DOING HERE.
- WELL, YOU SAID YOU
WANTED ME TO POSE FOR YOU
SO I THOUGHT YOU'D BE
HAPPY THAT I CAME HERE.
- AND WHAT EXACTLY
GAVE YOU THE IDEA
THAT I WANT YOU TO POSE FOR ME
WHILE LIVING IN MY HOUSE?
- ( crying ) IT'S BECAUSE
OF THE KISS, ISN'T IT?
YOU'RE MAD AT ME.
- HUH?
- YOU CAN'T EVEN STAND
TO LOOK AT ME ANYMORE.
- WHAT DID YOU DO
TO THIS POOR LITTLE THING?
- I HAVEN'T DONE ANYTHING
TO HER, GEEZ!
- ALL RIGHT.
LET'S ALL CALM DOWN.
WE JUST NEED TO ACCEPT
THAT THIS IS KOUHEI'S FAULT.
AND NO ONE ELSE'S.
- WHAT? I NEVER SAID
OR DID ANYTHING
TO THIS LITTLE NUT JOB!
- SINCE MY GRANDSON SAYS
HE'S NOT RESPONSIBLE FOR YOU,
I WILL BE.
DOES THAT SOUND LIKE A DEAL
TO YOU, YOUNG LADY?
- ( gasps )
- I CAN'T THANK YOU ENOUGH.
I PUT MYSELF IN YOUR CARE.
- GRAMPS, YOU GOTTA BE
KIDDING ME! YOU CAN'T DO THIS!
NOW WHAT?
- SEE, BIG BROTHER?
I TOLD YOU I'D MAKE
YOU MY SLAVE.
- ( growls )
I AM NOT YOUR SLAVE!
- Ryuuhei: SO, SHE'S NOT HUMAN.
- Seiji: THAT'S RIGHT.
IT LOOKS LIKE THINGS ARE GONNA
GET INTERESTING AROUND HERE.
- Ryuuhei: ( chuckles )
YOU CAN SAY THAT AGAIN.
THAT YOUNG LADY COULD
COMPLICATE THINGS QUITE A BIT.
- Hazuki: RIDDLE TIME AGAIN,
BIG BROTHER!
THIS IS AN EASY ONE.
WHERE DO ANIMALS GO
WHEN THEY LOSE THEIR TAILS?
YOU'D HAVE TO BE REALLY DUMB
NOT TO GET THIS ONE.
READY? GO! FULL, FULL,
FULL MOON! TIME'S UP!
NEXT TIME ON MOON PHASE,
EPISODE THREE.
"BIG BROTHER,
LET'S LIVE TOGETHER."
WANNA KNOW THE ANSWER, DUMMY?
WHEN ANIMALS LOSE THEIR TAILS,
THEY GO TO THE RETAIL STORE!
- ( giggles )