- ( sighs ) MADE IT.
I BROUGHT US
SOME MEAT DUMPLINGS, KAORU.
I GOT THE VERY LAST TWO.
HEY, KAORU, WHERE'D YOU GO?
SHE'S NOT BACK AT THE PLATFORM?
WHERE WERE YOU?
YOU WERE SUPPOSED TO STAY HERE
AND WATCH OUR STUFF FOR A WHILE.
- I HAD TO DO SOMETHING.
- WHAT DO YOU MEAN YOU
HAD TO DO SOMETHING?
- ( clicking )
- ( gasps )
- Announcer: LADIES
AND GENTLEMEN,
WE'RE INVESTIGATING THE
SOURCE OF THE POWER FAILURE.
PLEASE REMAIN SEATED.
- I HOPE IT ISN'T
SOMETHING MAJOR.
IF THE TRAIN'S DELAYED WE WON'T
GET BACK TO KYOTO TONIGHT.
OH, KAORU, NO!
DID YOU CAUSE THE POWER FAILURE?
- UH...
- DON'T LIE!
- ( laughing )
- ( theme song playing )
- ( singing in Japanese )
- WE'D APPRECIATE IT IF
YOU'D LET US STAY FOR THE NIGHT
SINCE OUR TRAIN GOT DELAYED.
- IF YOU DON'T MIND.
- OH, SO YOU THINK YOU CAN JUST
SHOW UP ON OUR DOORSTEP, HUH?
- NO, OF COURSE WE DON'T MIND.
MAKE YOURSELVES
AT HOME, YOU TWO.
- DON'T SAY THAT!
- THANKS, BIG BROTHER,
WE WON'T BE ANY TROUBLE.
- NOT AT ALL, WE PROMISE.
- I'M SURE YOU WON'T.
- BROTHER SEIJI IS STILL
AT THE HOSPITAL
WITH GRANDPA RYUUHEI?
- TURNS OUT GRAMPS HAD SOME
SCRAPES TOO FROM THAT NIGHT.
HE JUST WAITED 'TIL I WAS IN THE
CLEAR TO SAY ANYTHING, OLD GOOF.
- AND HOW ARE YOU FEELING?
- ME? OKAY.
- DON'T WORRY ABOUT HIM.
HE'S DOING JUST FINE!
- REALLY? I THOUGHT THE DOCTOR
SAID TO TAKE IT EASY
FOR A LITTLE WHILE.
- SHUT YOUR TRAP, SHORT STUFF!
- WELL, THAT WASN'T VERY NICE.
- ARE YOU STILL IN ANY PAIN?
- NOT REALLY, AS LONG AS
I DON'T MOVE AROUND TOO MUCH.
- WELL, LET ME KNOW
IF YOU NEED ANYTHING, OKAY?
- IF HE NEEDS ANYTHING,
I WILL GET IT FOR HIM!
- HEY, KOUHEI, DID YOU HEAR
SOMETHING JUST NOW?
- ( both growling )
- ON YOUR MARKS! LET'S MAKE
THIS A CLEAN FIGHT, LADIES.
- DON'T ENCOURAGE THEM, HAIJI.
- AW.
- I THOUGHT YOU'D LIKE THIS.
- THANKS, KAORU,
YOU JUST READ MY MIND.
I DIDN'T KNOW THAT
WAS ONE OF YOUR GIFTS.
- WAIT A MINUTE, THIS IS OUR
TEA. SHE STOLE THAT TEA FROM US!
- ( sighs ) COME ON, HAZUKI.
- IF THESE GRUBBY FREAKS START
GRUBBY-HANDING OUR STUFF
AND MOVING IT ALL AROUND,
WE'LL NEVER BE ABLE TO FIND
ANYTHING IN THE KITCHEN AGAIN!
- YEAH, LIKE WE CAN
FIND ANYTHING IN THERE NOW.
- HE DOES HAVE A POINT, MASTER.
- Haiji: TRUE OR FALSE. THE
CHOPSTICKS ARE IN THE DRAWER.
- Kouhei: FALSE. FOUND 'EM
IN THE FRIDGE THIS MORNING.
- AND THE SOY SAUCE.
ON THE TABLE, CORRECT?
- IN THE FOYER
UNDER AN ORNAMENTAL FAN.
- A WORLD OF PAIN!
- ( both exclaim )
- ANYWAY, IT'S NOT REALLY
YOUR KITCHEN AT ALL,
IS IT, LITTLE MISS MOOCH?
- DID SHE JUST... DID YOU
JUST CALL ME A MOOCH?
- WELL HEY, WHAT DO YOU KNOW. IT
DOES UNDERSTAND HUMAN LANGUAGES.
- THAT'S PRETTY GOOD
FOR A DEMON.
- ( gasps )
HOLD IT, FOUR-EYES!
WHAT DID YOU JUST SAY TO ME?
- ( whimpers )
- BROTHER KOUHEI!
THE DEMON-GIRL'S
YELLING AT MY SISTER.
- SAY "DEMON"
ONE MORE TIME, SPELL-GIRL!
- HAZUKI, CUT IT OUT.
- DON'T YOU SAY "CUT IT OUT"
TO ME, YOU TRAITOR!
YOU'RE MY SLAVE
AND YOU'RE TAKING
THEIR STUPID SIDE AGAINST ME!
- IT'S NOT LIKE THAT. COME ON!
- FINE! THEN DO
WHATEVER YOU WANT!
MAYBE THEY CAN STAY.
THEY'RE PROBABLY BETTER
COOKS THAN ME ANYWAY.
- HAZUKI, PLEASE, DON'T BE
LIKE THAT OH, WHOA, OUCH!
- ( gasps )
- ( gasps ) KOUHEI!
- ( whimpers )
- DO YOU FEEL DIZZY?
- DO YOU NEED TO LIE DOWN?
- SHOULD I GO GET A DOCTOR?
- WHERE DOES IT HURT?
- All: FEEL BETTER?
- OH, DEFINITELY.
THE THERMOMETER REALLY
DID THE TRICK, THANKS.
- All: REALLY? I'LL GO
GET ANOTHER ONE!
- GET BACK HERE, I WAS JUST
KIDDING! AND QUIT FREAKIN' OUT!
IT'S NOT LIKE I'M AN INVALID,
GIRLS. I JUST NEED SOME REST.
- Haiji: THIS'LL
KNOCK HIM OUT, MASTER!
- WHAT IS THAT STUFF?
- ( grunting )
- All: WHOA!
- I HOPE YOU DON'T THINK
I'M DRINKING THAT, HAIJI!
- IT'S GOOD FOR YA.
PUTS HAIR ON YOUR CHEST.
- I FEEL BETTER! REALLY!
- Man: HAVE A GOOD NIGHT!
- ( motorcycle engine starts )
- All: WOW!
- REAL PIZZA DELIVERED RIGHT TO
YOUR DOOR. IT'S JUST BEAUTIFUL.
-IT'S THE MOST
BEAUTIFUL THING EVER.
- AND JUST THINK. IF WE'D GONE
HOME WE NEVER WOULD'VE SEEN IT.
- GOOD THING OUR TRAIN
BROKE DOWN.
- I'VE NEVER SEEN ANYONE
GET SO EXCITED OVER PIZZA.
YOU TWO ARE EASILY IMPRESSED.
- ( both giggling )
- THEY'RE COUNTRY
BUMPKINS, KOUHEI.
- ( scoffs )
- ( whimpers )
- WOULD YA LAY OFF THEM ALREADY?
JUST FOCUS ON DINNER.
- ALL RIGHT, THEN! HAIJI
AND I CLAIM ONE WHOLE PIZZA!
- ( snoring )
- OH, MY I BELIEVE YOUR
SHIKIGAMI'S GONE AND
GOTTEN HERSELF A LITTLE
SLOSHED, HAZUKI.
LOOKS LIKE WE COUNTRY BUMPKINS
AREN'T THE ONLY
UNCIVILIZED ONES, HUH?
- WHY DON'T YOU WAKE UP
AND DEFEND YOURSELF?
YOU'RE EMBARRASSING ME,
YOU LUSH!
- ( laughs ) TAKE A
LOOK AT THIS, KAORU,
IT'S A DRUNKEN LITTLE ELF!
WHAT'S WRONG, KAORU?
WHAT IS IT?
WHAT ARE YOU CRYING FOR, KID?
ARE YOU OKAY?
- ( whimpering )
- KAORU, WHAT'S THE MATTER?
- ARE YOU OKAY?
COME ON, TALK TO US!
- ( continues whimpering )
- WHAT IS IT?
- ARE YOU CHOKING?
YOU ALLERGIC? WHAT'S WRONG?
- IT'S JUST THAT...
THIS PIZZA'S SO GOOD!
- ( sighs )
IT IS OUR FIRST ONE.
- OH. WELL, I'M GLAD
YOU'RE LIKIN' IT.
( laughs )
- CRYING OVER PIZZA?
SUCH A PATHETIC BACKWATER
THING TO DO. WHAT A HEADCASE...
- WE'RE BOTH GLAD
YOU LIKE IT, KAORU.
SO I TAKE IT YOU WANT
ANOTHER SLICE.
- ( all laughing )
- YOU KNOW, YOU'RE PRETTY LUCKY
TO BE ENGAGED TO KOUHEI.
- ( giggling )
( screams )
- OH, RELAX. YOUR GLASSES
FELL OFF, THAT'S ALL.
- ( sniffles )
- COME ON! YOU'RE NOT GONNA
CRY AGAIN, ARE YOU?
- I DON'T KNOW. MAYBE!
- YOU KNOW, IT WOULDN'T KILL
YOU TO BE A LITTLE NICER
TO THE TWINS, BRAT.
- I DON'T MEAN TO BE
SO RUDE ALL THE TIME,
BUT THEY KEEP
PISSING ME OFF.
YOU JUST NEVER NOTICE IT
WHEN THEY DO MEAN STUFF TO ME.
- THEY'RE STILL
JUST KIDS, HAZUKI.
OH. WAIT. SO ARE YOU.
- HEY, I'M WAY MORE MATURE
THAN THEY ARE!
TAKE THIS STUFF TO THE
BATHROOM FOR ME, WOULD YA?
- WHAT? YOU WANT ME
TO BRING THE ENEMY CLEAN TOWELS?
FAT CHANCE, MISTER.
YOU'RE THE SLAVE. YOU TAKE 'EM!
- JUST TAKE THEM, HAZ, OKAY?
I DON'T FEEL TOO GOOD.
I THINK I OVERDID IT
A BIT TONIGHT.
- BUT YOU'RE GONNA BE
OKAY THOUGH, AREN'T YOU?
- YEAH, I'M SURE I'LL BE
JUST FINE IN THE MORNING.
I'M FEELIN' A LITTLE BIT
LIGHTHEADED IS ALL.
I THINK I'LL TURN IN EARLY.
- THEN SLEEP IN TOMORROW.
- THE TWINS WANNA
STOP IN AND SEE GRAMPS
AT THE HOSPITAL TOMORROW
MORNING BEFORE THEY LEAVE.
THEY'RE GONNA NEED SOMEONE
TO TAKE THEM OUT THERE.
- YOU'RE NOT SUPPOSED TO
MOVE AROUND TOO MUCH.
- DON'T WORRY. I'LL TAKE THE
CAR. I'M SURE IT'LL BE FI...
OKAY, THAT DOES IT,
DEFINITELY TIME FOR BED.
- TOMORROW...
TOMORROW IT HAPPENS.
- YOU REALLY DON'T HAVE TO
TAKE US, BROTHER KOUHEI.
- I'M DRIVING A CAR.
HOW HARD CAN IT BE?
( groans )
- STANDING UP SHOULD
BE EASY, TOO.
- ( whimpers )
- WELL, I CAN'T HAVE YOU TWO
GETTING LOST OUT THERE, CAN I?
TOKYO'S A DANGEROUS CITY.
- BROTHER KOUHEI!
- HUH?
- WHAT THE HELL?
- IT'S A CAT.
- ARE YOU SURE, SISTER?
- OF COURSE I'M A CAT. WHAT DO
I LOOK LIKE, A TOASTER OVEN?
- WAIT A MINUTE. IS THAT...
- THE DEMON-GIRL?
- DON'T CALL ME "DEMON-GIRL"!
- HAZUKI, WHY ARE YOU OUTSIDE?
AND WHAT THE HELL
ARE YOU WEARING?
- I'M WEARING MY
ANTI-SUN CAT SUIT!
( imitates meowing )
NOW I CAN TAKE THE LOBOTOMY
TWINS TO THE HOSPITAL
AND THE SUN CAN'T GET TO ME.
SO YOU CAN STAY HOME.
- SO YOU'RE A...
- A CAT!
- JUST CHECKING.
- I'LL BET THAT THING COMES
COMPLETE WITH FLEAS
AND HEARTWORM.
- I HAD TO MAKE A COSTUME
OVERNIGHT! WHAT DO YOU EXPECT?
GLITTER AND SEQUINS?
NOW YOU GET BACK TO BED, KOUHEI!
BRATTY AND DUMMY, YOU FOLLOW ME.
- ALL RIGHT, HAZUKI.
HOLD ON, ONE MORE QUESTION.
- NOW WHAT?
- DO YOU, UH, KNOW
WHERE YOU'RE GOING?
- THE HOSPITAL, DUH!
- THE HOSPITAL'S IN
THE OTHER DIRECTION.
- MAYBE YOU SHOULD
HAVE MADE A COSTUME
WITH BIGGER
EYE-HOLES, GENIUS.
- THERE ARE NO EYE HOLES!
IF THERE WERE EYE HOLES I'D
BE BURNED TO A CRISP BY NOW!
- SO HOW DO YOU PLAN
TO LEAD THEM ANYWHERE?
- I THINK "PLAN" MIGHT BE
TOO STRONG OF A WORD HERE.
- I THINK YOU'RE RIGHT.
- HAIJI, I NEED YOU!
- HERE! WHAT'S UP?
- I WANT TO GO TO THE HOSPITAL.
- RIGHT-O!
- HIKARU, KAORU.
FOLLOW ME, PLEASE.
AND HURRY UP!
- ( both sigh )
- FINE.
- IF HAIJI'S LEADING US THEN
WHAT DO WE EVEN NEED HER FOR?
- SOME KIND OF PUNISHMENT?
- NOW, STAY ALERT!
WHEN I SAY, "CHECK IN,"
I WANT YOU TO SAY
YOU'RE STILL WITH ME.
- CHECK IN!
- ( both ) WE'RE STILL WITH YOU.
- STILL WITH YOU!
- ( sighs ) I HOPE THEY
DON'T KILL EACH OTHER.
- Kinkel: IT'S TRUE OF EVEN
THE MOST STUBBORN MARES.
EVENTUALLY THEY ALL BREAK.
- MAN, IT'S HOT! WHAT'S THE
TEMPERATURE TODAY, ANYWAY?
- HOTTEST DAY THIS WINTER,
BUT THERE'S A COOL BREEZE
FOR PEOPLE NOT IN CAT SUITS.
THINK ABOUT SOMETHING
ELSE. WANNA PLAY I SPY?
- NO.
- ( indistinct chatter )
- ( people laughing )
- EVERYBODY'S STARING.
- I'M SO EMBARRASSED.
- HIKARU? KAORU?
ALMOST TIME TO CHECK IN!
- DON'T CALL OUT OUR NAMES
LIKE THAT, IT'S HUMILIATING!
AT LEAST WE REMEMBERED TO
PUT THAT INVISIBILITY
SPELL ON HAIJI.
IF PEOPLE COULD SEE HER
FLOATING AROUND IN FRONT OF US,
WHO KNOWS HOW THEY'D REACT?
IT'S BAD ENOUGH
WE'VE GOT A WALKING,
TALKING FRANKENSTEIN
CAT LEADING THE WAY!
- YOU'RE JUST BEING PARANOID.
NOBODY'S EVEN LOOKING!
- OF COURSE THEY'RE ALL LOOKING,
WHAT ARE YOU, FREAKING BLIND?
- ( people laughing )
- HEY, DO YOU HAVE ANY
EXTRA CHANGE IN THERE?
- I HAVE A LITTLE.
- WHOA, WHOA, WHOA,
WHOA, WHOA! HUH-UH.
YOU HAVE TO HAVE A TICKET
OR I CAN'T LET YOU THROUGH.
- BUT I'M A CAT!
- A CAT, HUH?
- YOU CAN'T EXPECT A CAT
TO CARRY AROUND LOOSE CHANGE.
- WELL, I EXPECT A LOT
FROM TALKING CATS.
- OH. MEOW.
- NICE TRY, KIDDO, BUT NO WAY.
- MEANIE.
- HERE, THIS IS FOR
THE CAT, OKAY?
- REALLY? YOU GUYS ARE ACTUALLY
GONNA PAY FOR THIS NUT-JOB?
- ONWARD! MEOW.
- WE'RE SORRY, SIR.
- THERE ARE PLACES FOR
PEOPLE LIKE YOU, YOU KNOW.
THEY HAVE PADDED WALLS!
- HIKARU! KAORU!
OVER HERE!
- STOP USING OUR REAL NAMES!
- HEY, I THINK THAT'S
THE HOSPITAL! WHAT IS IT?
- ( breathing heavily )
- YOU OKAY, MASTER?
- NO. I'M DYING!
- AW, WHAT'S THE MATTER,
DEMON-GIRL?
YOU HAVING TROUBLE KEEPING UP?
- ( grunts angrily )
- IT'S ALL RIGHT TO
ADMIT DEFEAT, YOU KNOW.
- HURRY UP, YOU LAZY BUMS!
LET'S GO!
MEOW, MEOW, MEOW! MEOW,
MEOW! MEOW, MEOW, MEOW!
- OKAY, SHE'S COMPLETELY INSANE.
- ( elevator bell dings )
- OH, SWEET AIR-CONDITIONING!
HEY, AREN'T YOU TWO FORGETTING
TO THANK ME FOR
BRINGING YOU HERE?
- SAY THANK YOU.
- HMPH!
- ( grunting )
COME ON, HIKARU.
SAY, "THANK YOU, HAZUKI."
- THANK YOU, HAZUKI.
- IT WAS MY PLEASURE, HIKARU.
- LET'S HAVE SOME JUICE, HAIJI.
- JUICE!
- I WONDER WHAT
THAT'S ALL ABOUT.
- I GUESS SOMEBODY ON THIS FLOOR
JUST TOOK A TURN FOR THE WORSE.
- All: OH, NO!
WHAT IF IT'S...
GRANDFATHER!
- OH, I'M SORRY, ARE YOU
RELATIVES OF HIS?
- WHAT HAPPENED?
WE THOUGHT THEY WERE
MINOR INJURIES...
- YES, WE THOUGHT SO TOO.
- HE LOOKS BAD.
- WILL HE BE OKAY?
- WHERE'S SEIJI MIDO?
- HUH? OH, YOU MEAN THE MAN
WHO WAS WITH HIM EARLIER?
HE LEFT A LITTLE WHILE AGO.
BEFORE ANY OF THIS HAPPENED.
- WHERE'RE YOU GOING?
- Kouhei: WHERE'S SEIJI?
- I DON'T KNOW. DO YOU THINK YOU
CAN MAKE IT UP HERE, KOUHEI?
- YEAH. I'LL BE THERE.
I'LL GET A TAXI OR SOMETHING.
- OKAY, BE CAREFUL.
OH, AND DO YOU HAVE SEIJI'S
CELL PHONE NUMBER?
I DON'T HAVE IT MEMORIZED.
- WHAT'S KOUHEI SAYING, HAZUKI?
- I'LL CALL.
- Operator: THE NUMBER
YOU ARE TRYING TO REACH
IS TEMPORARILY OUT OF RANGE.
PLEASE HANG UP AND TRY
YOUR CALL AT ANOTHER TIME.
- I CAN'T REACH SEIJI'S CELL.
- TELL US WHAT'S GOING ON.
- WAIT, I BET HE WENT TO THE
PUBLISHING HOUSE FOR A WHILE.
MAYBE I COULD FIND HIM THERE!
- LET ME GO, I CAN RUN FASTER!
- BUT DO YOU KNOW WHERE IT IS?
YOU STAY HERE WITH GRANDFATHER.
I'LL BE BACK WHEN I FIND HIM.
- BUT!
- HAIJI!
- COMING!
- SHE'S AWFULLY STUBBORN.
- OH, I FORGOT ABOUT THE HEAT!
I THINK IT'S EVEN HOTTER
THAN IT WAS BEFORE!
- I THINK YOU'RE RIGHT.
- OH, I'M GONNA FAINT!
NO! THIS IS NO TIME
TO WUSS OUT. LET'S GO, HAIJI!
- HANG ON FOR
SUPER WARP SPEED!
- AH! HAIJI! THAT'S TOO FAST,
I CAN'T KEEP UP!
SERIOUSLY, I'M GONNA FALL DOWN,
HAIJI! PLEASE! SLOW DOWN!
I CAN'T RUN IN THESE
STUPID CAT PAWS!
( screaming )
( groaning )
IT'S A GOOD THING
CATS HAVE NINE LIVES.
- HAZUKI, WE SAW YOU FALL,
YOU ALL RIGHT?
- OF COURSE I'M ALL RIGHT.
CATS ALWAYS LAND ON THEIR FEET.
NOW WHAT ARE YOU
DOING OUT HERE?
YOU'RE SUPPOSED TO
BE WITH GRANDFATHER,
NOT WORRYING ABOUT
SOME STUPID CAT!
ALL RIGHT. ENOUGH DILLYDALLYING.
IT'S TIME TO GO. WHERE'S HAIJI?
( groaning )
I'M OKAY. I'M OKAY.
HAIJI, ARE YOU THERE?
- UH-HUH.
- GOTTA FIND SEIJI.
GOTTA FIND SEIJI.
- JUST A MINUTE.
- LET HER HELP YOU, FIRST.
- I CALL ON SHINA-TO-BE,
GODDESS OF WIND.
LEND ME YOUR POWER.
GIVE ME YOUR BREATH.
- ( grunts )
- Haiji: A SHIKIGAMI!
- AH!
OH, THAT FEELS SO GOOD!
- HE'LL STAY WITH YOU UNTIL
YOU TAKE THE CAT SUIT OFF.
- HIS KI GIVES OFF
A KIND OF COOLING ENERGY.
- YOU SHOULD GET GOING NOW.
- I HAVE SOMETHING TO SAY FIRST.
THANK YOU.
- YOU'RE VERY WELCOME, HAZUKI.
- I FEEL THE COOL ENERGY! HAIJI!
- HERE WE GO AT
SUPER WARP SPEED!
- REGULAR WARP SPEED
IS FINE! HAIJI!
- ( both giggling )
- ALL RIGHT, WE SHOULD
PROBABLY GET BACK INSIDE.
- UH-HUH.
- ( breathing heavily )
- SO, YOU'D LIKE
TO SEE SEIJI MIDO?
- YES! IT'S URGENT!
- I, I SEE. URGENT.
AND MAY I ASK HOW YOU KNOW HIM?
- NO! JUST GET YOUR
SKINNY BUTT ON THE PHONE!
- YES, MA'AM.
I'LL CALL RIGHT AWAY.
- GRANDFATHER!
- IS HE ALL RIGHT?
- AH! SEIJI! HAZUKI! HELLO!
- BUT YOU WERE SO SICK BEFORE.
- HAZUKI TELLS ME YOU
TOOK A TURN FOR THE WORSE.
- ( laughs )
- WELL...
- IT WAS ALL AN ACT.
- Hazuki: AN ACT?
- YOUR TEMPERATURE LOOKS NORMAL.
NOW I DON'T WANT ANY MORE
FALSE ALARMS LIKE THIS.
YOU'RE TOO OLD
TO BE FAKING SICK.
- ( laughs ) RIGHT.
- GOOD LUCK WITH THIS ONE, GUYS.
- SOMEBODY TELL ME
WHAT'S GOING ON.
- GRANDPA RYUUHEI HAS
THE HOTS FOR THAT NURSE.
- HE WANTED TO MEET THE NURSE
WHO WAS ON DUTY TODAY,
SO NATURALLY HE FAKED
GOING INTO A COMA.
- ( laughs )
I HAD NO IDEA EVERYONE WOULD
TAKE IT SO SERIOUSLY, THOUGH.
WHAT A LARK!
WHAT A BUNCH OF FOOLS.
YOU ALL THOUGHT
I WAS DYING, DIDN'T YOU?
- WE HAD OUR HOPES, ANYWAY.
- DOESN'T HE EVER TAKE
ANYTHING SERIOUSLY?
- NOT REALLY. NO.
- EXCEPT NURSES.
- ( continues laughing )
- HAZUKI? YOU DOING OKAY, KID?
- YOU'RE LOOKING A LITTLE SHAKEN
UP, CHILD, ARE YOU ALL RIGHT?
- ( all exclaim )
- GRANDFATHER RYUUHEI!
- UH, YES, CHILD?
- I'M GLAD THAT YOU'RE
FEELING SO MUCH BETTER.
- ( stuttering ) THANKS.
- AND THAT'S ALL I HAVE TO SAY.
( evil laughter )
- WHAT THE...
- I THINK I NEED ANOTHER BEDPAN.
- EWW!
- SO, TAKE CARE.
- YEAH. YOU TOO.
- WE'LL SEE YOU.
- I THINK SHE KINDA
LIKES YOU NOW.
- BACK AT YA!
- ( all giggling )
- ( giggling )
- WELL...
KOUHEI IS STILL HER FUTURE
HUSBAND, AND NOT YOUR SLAVE,
SO DON'T GO GETTING
ANY LONG TERM IDEAS, GOT IT?
- YES. THAT'S RIGHT.
- AND OUR NAME FOR YOU HASN'T
CHANGED. IT'S STILL "DEMON"!
- KOUHEI IS AND WILL
ALWAYS BE MY SLAVE!
AND DON'T CALL ME A DEMON!
- ( theme song playing )
- ( singing in Japanese )
- Hikaru: BROTHER KOUHEI! LOOK!
YOU GET A NEW CAMERA
IN THE NEXT EPISODE!
- I DO? WHAT KIND? WHERE?
- Hikaru: JUST KIDDING!
- Kaoru: JUST KIDDING!
- Hikaru: OH, NOW DON'T LOOK
LIKE THAT. IT WAS JUST A JOKE.
UH-OH. HE REALLY IS MAD. YOU'D
BETTER APOLOGIZE TOO, KAORU.
- I'M SORRY, BROTHER KOUHEI.
I DIDN'T MEAN TO MAKE YOU ANGRY.
- DOESN'T LOOK LIKE IT'S
WORKING. HE'S STILL MAD AT US.
LET'S JUST SAY THE NAME OF THE
EPISODE AND GET OUT OF HERE.
- Kaoru: EPISODE 12.
"I'LL NEVER FORGIVE HIM!"
IS HE STILL MAD?
( whimpers )