- ( Kouhei breathing heavily )
- ( theme song playing )
- ( singing in Japanese )
- IT REALLY IS OVER, ISN'T IT?
( Hazuki speaking )
- Hmm...
- KIND OF WENT OVERBOARD
WITH THE DECORATIONS,
DIDN'T THEY?
- Hazuki: ARE YOU
DEAF NOW, DUMMY?
I SAID THAT GOES OVER HERE!
- WHAT? YOU DID NOT.
- I MOST CERTAINLY DID,
I SAID IT GOES ON THIS SHELF
HERE! RIGHT BEHIND ME!
- YOU DIDN'T SAY THAT!
- DID TOO!
- YOU DID NOT!
- I KNOW FOR A FACT YOU DIDN'T!
- WELL I TOLD YOU NOW!
- EXCELLENT, SO YOU ADMIT
YOU DIDN'T BEFORE!
- I'M NOT ADMITTING ANYTHING,
MORON!
BUT SOMEONE HAD TO BE
MATURE ENOUGH
TO DROP IT AND YOU
OBVIOUSLY WOULDN'T!
- Haiji: AT THIS RATE
YOU'LL NEVER GET YOUR ANTIQUE
SHOP REOPENED, GRANDPA.
SHOULDN'T WE MAKE THEM STOP?
- OH, LET THEM BE.
THESE ARGUMENTS
ARE
HOW THEY SHOW THEIR FEELINGS
FOR EACH OTHER.
THAT'S MINE
AND ELFRIEDE'S CONCLUSION.
- THAT'S RIGHT,
IT'S ALL FOR LOVE.
- LOVE?
- YOU'RE ARGUING THIS TOO?
- 'CAUSE YOU'RE WRONG!
- AM NOT! SHUT UP!
- ARE TOO!
- THAT'S WEIRD. -
Kouhei: NOT THAT I CARE,
BUT IT DOESN'T MAKE SENSE!
- Hazuki: SHE WEARS THEM, OKAY!
- Kouhei: AH, COME ON!
- SHE DOES WEAR UNDERWEAR.
I'VE SEEN THEM MYSELF!
- ( exclaims )
OKAY! WHAT ON EARTH
ARE YOU FIGHTING ABOUT NOW?
- ( both sighing heavily )
- HAIJI! SHOW HIM
WHAT'S UNDER YOUR OUTFIT!
- HEY! THAT ISN'T APPROPRIATE!
( screaming ) STOP! A SHIKIGAMI
HAS A RIGHT TO PRIVACY!
- WELL, THE SHOP'S FINALLY READY
FOR ITS GRAND REOPENING,
THAT'S GOOD NEWS RIGHT?
- RIGHT.
- ( grumbling )
- AH, HAIJI. DON'T BE MAD,
WE SAID WE WERE SORRY.
- SHUT UP, SLAVE-BOY!
I'VE NEVER BEEN SO
EMBARRASSED IN MY LIFE!
IF I COULD, I'D VANISH
AND NEVER COME BACK!
- WELL, YOU KNOW,
I COULD DO THAT FOR YOU.
- YOU CAN'T USE YOUR POWER!
MY MASTER TOLD ME!
- AND YOU BELIEVE THAT?
DO YOU REALLY WANT TO RISK IT?
- ( squealing )
- GOODNIGHT, EVERYBODY.
( yawning )
- WE'LL SEE HOW SLAVE BOY FEELS
WHEN HE WAKES UP TOMORROW
AND SEES I'VE WRITTEN "BOOBY"
ON HIS FEET
IN MAGIC INK THAT WON'T
EVER COME OFF!
"B-O-O" ON HIS RIGHT FOOT.
AND"B-Y" ON HIS LEFT!
- ( sighing )
- IS IT REALLY TRUE
WHAT HAIJI SAID ABOUT HIS POWER?
- HMM?
- HAS HE REALLY LOST
THE USE OF HIS JAGAN?
- Ryuuhei: JUDGING FROM
WHAT I SENSE OF HIS KI,
IT'S TRUE.
HE DOESN'T HAVE THE ABILITY
THAT HE DID AT HIS PEAK.
- Elfriede: DID HE EXHAUST IT
IN THAT FINAL BATTLE?
- NO. KOUHEI'S JAGAN
IS LIKE A BOTTOMLESS WELL.
BUT HE'S SEALED IT
BACK UP, HIMSELF.
- SEALED IT? BUT WHY?
- SIMPLE. SO HIS RELATIONSHIP
WITH HAZUKI COULD STAY THE SAME.
- ( humming )
( gasping )
( screaming )
- ( toilet flushing )
- ( growling )
- Hazuki: YOU IDIOT!
- WHAT'RE YOU DOING IN HERE?
- Kouhei: WHAT DO YOU THINK?
I HAD TO GO TO THE
BATHROOM, OKAY?
- Hazuki: YOU SHOULD HAVE TOLD
ME YOU WERE IN HERE ALREADY!
YOU KNOW I TAKE MY BATH
AT NIGHT! IT'S MY ROUTINE!
- WELL, EXCUSE ME!
- YOU HID IN HERE ON PURPOSE!
YOU WERE SNEAKING
A PEAK, YOU PERV!
- OH, PLEASE.
- YOU'RE MAD AT ME
SO THIS IS HOW YOU GET ME BACK!
BY SPYING ON ME LIKE SOME
KIND OF CREEPY STALKER!
- YOU'RE CRAZY. WAIT 'TIL
YOU'VE ACTUALLY MATURED
BEFORE YOU ACCUSE ME OF THAT.
- WHAT? HOW DARE YOU SAY THAT,
YOU JERK! I'M INCREDIBLY MATURE!
( sneezing )
I WAS FINALLY IN A HAPPY MOOD
AND THEN KOUHEI HAD TO MESS
IT UP ALL OVER AGAIN!
DORK, IDIOT! DUMMY!
- Kouhei: YOU'RE CRAZY. WAIT
'TIL YOU'VE ACTUALLY MATURED
BEFORE YOU ACCUSE ME OF THAT.
- ( screaming )
- ( Hazuki grunting )
- ( gasping )
- Kouhei: JUST SAY SOMETHING,
HAZ.
ARE YOU REALLY STILL MAD AT ME
ABOUT LAST NIGHT?
- Ryuuhei: WHAT'D YOU
DO THIS TIME, KOUHEI?
- Kouhei: NOTHING,
THAT'S MY POINT,
BUT SHE'S
CONVINCED I'M A CREEP.
- Ryuuhei: AND WHY
WOULD SHE THINK THAT?
- ( scoffing ) SLAVE BOY
WAS HIDING LIKE A NINJA
IN THE RESTROOM
WHILE MY MASTER
WAS TAKING A BATH
SO HE COULD SEE HER
IN HER BIRTHDAY SUIT!
- THAT ISN'T TRUE!
WHY ARE YOU TRYING TO
MAKE THINGS WORSE
WHEN YOU KNOW IT WAS COMPLETELY
ACCIDENTAL?
- FIRST THE UNDERWEAR TALK,
NOW THIS!
IT IS TRUE!
AND DON'T LECTURE MY SHIKIGAMI!
- WELL, I WOULDN'T HAVE TO
IF SHE WASN'T
SPREADING YOUR LIES!
- OH, KOUHEI.
HIDING IN THE BATHROOM?
HOW ON EARTH COULD YOU
DO SUCH A THING?
- SERIOUSLY, THAT'S PRETTY SICK.
- NOBODY WAS HIDING ANYWHERE!
I WAS JUST USING THE
FREAKING BATHROOM!
WHY WOULD I WANT TO
SEE HER NAKED ANYWAY?
SHE'S JUST A KID!
- ( growling )
- ( all gasping )
- I'M DONE!
- HEY, HAZ?
- HMM?
- YOU'VE GOT SOME RICE
ON YOUR FACE.
- IT'S ON PURPOSE!
IT'S A NEW FASHION TREND!
- Kouhei: WHATEVER.
- ( all sighing )
- ( exclaiming )
- AND I THOUGHT THAT FIGHT
WITH JEDA WAS BAD.
- ELFRIEDE?
- OH. HEY, HAZUKI.
- SORRY ABOUT MY LITTLE TANTRUM.
TELL GRANDPA THAT I'M
SORRY TOO, OKAY?
- EVERY FAMILY HAS THEIR FIGHTS.
- YEAH. I GUESS. OH, I FORGOT!
HAVE YOU HEARD IF SEIJI'S HAD
LUCK WITH HIS SEARCH YET?
- NOT SO FAR.
- HMM.
HE HASN'T BEEN ABLE TO FIND HER?
- ARE YOU WORRIED ABOUT HER?
IS THAT WHY YOU'RE ASKING?
- NOT REALLY.
- SHE IS YOUR HALF SISTER,
AFTER ALL.
- THAT'S WHAT SHE'S CLAIMING,
ANYWAY, BUT THERE'S NO PROOF.
SHE COULD'VE MADE IT ALL UP.
- Elfriede: IS THAT
WHAT YOU BELIEVE?
- WHEN THE SMOKE CLEARED
AFTER THE FIGHT, SHE WAS GONE.
ARTE CAN GO WHEREVER SHE WANTS
THAT MAKES HER HAPPY.
I DON'T CARE.
- ( laughs )
- ( gasping )
- EVERY ABLE PSYCHIC
IN THE MIDO CLAN
IS LOOKING FOR HER RIGHT NOW.
THEY UNDERSTAND
SHE WASN'T THE REAL ENEMY.
JUST BE PATIENT.
ARTE CAN'T STAY HIDDEN FOREVER.
I'M CERTAIN OF IT, HAZUKI.
THEY'LL FIND HER SOON.
- IT WOULD BE GOOD TO KNOW,
I GUESS.
- YOU CARE ABOUT HER.
- I DO NOT! YOU CAN BE
SO DUMB SOMETIMES!
- ( laughing )
MY MISTAKE.
- ( dog barking )
- THEY SHOULD ALL BE ARRIVING
ANY MINUTE NOW.
- PERFECT TIMING.
- YOU SHOULD STEP OUTSIDE,
HAZUKI. THE MOON IS BEAUTIFUL.
- YEAH, I KNOW. IT'S FULL,
I SAW IT ALREADY.
MY TEETH ARE TINGLING
LIKE CRAZY.
OF ALL THE NIGHTS,
WHY'D THE MOON HAVE
TO PICK THIS ONE?
- ( grunting )
- AND THE WAR RAGES ON...
- WHO WANTS TO PARTY?
- OH! HI, HIROMI!
- GLAD YOU COULD COME.
HOW DO YOU LIKE THE HOUSE?
- OH, IT LOOKS
JUST LIKE THE OLD ONE!
LIKE THE FIRE
NEVER EVEN HAPPENED!
- Both: GOOD EVENING, FAMILY!
- OH, HEY!
( laughing )
- WHAT'S UP, GIRLS?
- WE'RE SO HAPPY YOU HAD TIME
TO COME AND VISIT.
- SO ARE WE!
AND WE BROUGHT GIFTS, TOO!
THERE'S PLUM SAKE
FROM MASTER YAYOI,
AND BRAISED VEGETABLES
FROM GRANDMOTHER KOHARU.
- SHE MAKES, LIKE, THE BEST
BRAISED VEGETABLES EVER!
- Hikaru: SHE SAID
SHE ADDED EXTRA KELP,
JUST FOR YOU.
- Hazuki: AWESOME!
- HAVEN'T THOSE TWO
EXPRESSED ENOUGH LOVE
FOR THIS WEEK?
- HEY. WHAT'RE YOU DOING
DOWN THERE, KAORU?
- ( meowing )
- ( all gasping )
- ( chuckling ) WELL,
THAT'S AN INTERESTING LOOK.
- IT'S JUST SOMETHING
I PUT TOGETHER.
DO YOU LIKE IT, KOUHEI?
- OH, DEAR.
PRAISE HER, KOUHEI!
RIGHT NOW! PRAISE HER GOOD!
- THAT DOESN'T LOOK SAFE.
- IT'S NICE TO SEE YOU'RE
STICKING UP FOR YOUR SISTER,
HIKARU, BUT THERE'S NO NEED.
SHE LOOKS CUTE! HONESTLY!
- ( meowing )
- I CAN TELL THIS IS
GOING TO BE A GREAT NIGHT.
- ( meowing )
- HEY, HAIJI. YEAH, I KNOW.
IT'S NO FUN IN YOUR CAT FORM.
YOU KNOW THE RULES
WITH HIROMI.
BUT SHE'S DRINKING, YOU SEE?
ONCE SHE'S GOOD AND TIPSY
YOU CAN SWITCH BACK AGAIN.
- ( cat meowing )
- HAVE YOU HEARD FROM SEIJI,
HIKARU?
- I TALKED TO HIM
A LITTLE WHILE AGO.
HE SHOULD BE ON HIS WAY OVER.
- Ryuuhei: OH, REALLY?
THAT'S GOOD NEWS.
- YOU MEAN IT?
I DIDN'T THINK SEIJI WOULD HAVE
TIME TO STOP BY.
SINCE HE'S SO BUSY
SEARCHING ALL OVER JAPAN
FOR ARTE AND EVERYTHING.
- ( both gasping )
- YOU HAVEN'T HEARD YET?
- NO, HEARD WHAT?
- OH. I HAVEN'T TOLD KOUHEI
OR HAZUKI YET.
I DIDN'T THINK SEIJI WOULD COME.
- WHAT'RE YOU GUYS
TALKING ABOUT?
TELL US WHAT?
- HOPE I HAVEN'T MISSED
THE MAIN COURSE.
- WELL, THIS ROOM
JUST GOT HOTTER! HA!
- SOMEBODY CUT HER OFF.
- SO, DID YOU
BRING HER WITH YOU, SEIJI?
- YES.
- WHAT?
- WAIT, WHO ARE YOU
TALKING ABOUT?
- COME IN. DON'T BE SHY.
- ( gasping )
- ARTE.
- LUNA.
- ( chattering )
- I DON'T UNDERSTAND, GRANDPA,
WHY DIDN'T YOU TELL ME
SEIJI HAD FOUND HER?
- TO PROTECT YOU, HAZUKI.
- Seiji: TRUTH IS I'VE HAD HER
FOR A WHILE.
BUT I NEEDED TO
OBSERVE HER FIRST.
- HUNGRY?
- Hazuki: WHAT FOR?
- HE HAD TO SEE IF ARTE'S
TRUE NATURE WAS GOOD OR EVIL.
- THAT'S RIGHT. I BROUGHT HER
HERE
NOW THAT I'M SURE SHE
MEANS US NO HARM.
SHE'S JUST LONELY AND HURTING.
- SO WHERE DID YOU FIND HER
AFTER THE BATTLE?
- THE MIDO HOUSE IN KYOTO.
- REALLY? BUT I THOUGHT
IT WAS A WRECK NOW.
- WELL, IT'S SEEN BETTER DAYS,
I CAN SAY THAT MUCH.
- ALL ALONE.
- I TOOK HER TO WHERE THE
MAIN BRANCH OF THE FAMILY
IS STAYING NOW AND
HAD THEM KEEP HER.
BUT SHE WOULDN'T OPEN
UP TO ANY OF US.
NOT TO MASTER YAYOI,
OR TO GRANDMOTHER KOHARU,
OR EVEN TO THE TWINS.
- AFTER ALL SHE'S BEEN THROUGH
SHE PROBABLY DOESN'T WANT
TO TRUST ANYBODY.
- Seiji: ISOLATION CAN WARP
A PERSON'S MIND.
I'VE EXPERIENCED THAT FIRSTHAND.
- Ryuuhei:
WE ALL HAVE, AT TIMES.
- WEEKS GO BY
WITHOUT SEEING ANYONE.
PLAYING ALONE. EATING ALONE.
IT ISN'T EASY.
- WE'RE HOPING YOU'RE THE ONE
WHO CAN OPEN
THE CHILD'S HEART, HAZUKI.
ARE YOU UP TO THAT CHALLENGE?
- WHAT CAN I DO?
- Arte: YUM!
- ( all gasping )
- PLEASE HELP ME.
- ARTE!
- ( laughing )
- I DON'T KNOW WHAT'S GOING ON,
BUT I'M LIKING IT!
- WHAT DO YOU THINK
YOU'RE DOING KISSING HIM?
- IT'S A FULL MOON TONIGHT.
- I KNOW THAT, BELIEVE ME I DO,
BUT THAT DOESN'T MEAN YOU CAN
GO AROUND AND...
- ( screaming )
- OH, NOT YOU TOO, ELFRIEDE.
- ( exclaiming ) NOW THIS IS
A GOOD PARTY!
- ARE YOU INSANE?
- I'M TERRIBLY SORRY, HAZUKI,
I KNOW THIS ISN'T
APPROPRIATE BEHAVIOR,
BUT WHEN I SAW ARTE DOING IT
I COULDN'T HELP MYSELF.
- WHY DON'T YOU KISS GRANDPA
IF YOU'RE SO HUNGRY?
- ME? YEAH!
THAT ISN'T A BAD IDEA.
- YOU KNOW I CAN'T POSSIBLY
DO THAT.
- AND WHY NOT?
- BECAUSE IF I KISSED RYUUHEI
HE WOULD BECOME
MY OBEDIENT SLAVE,
FOLLOWING ME AROUND
LIKE SOME MINDLESS ANIMAL.
OUR DEAR KOHEI,
ON THE OTHER HAND,
IS THE VAMPIRE'S LOVER.
SO I CAN KISS HIM
WITH NO EFFECT.
- ACTUALLY, BEING A SLAVE
SOUNDS PRETTY GOOD.
- I DON'T CARE!
KOHEI'S MY SLAVE
AND I'M NOT GONNA SHARE HIM!
- WRONG, FANG-HEAD!
KAORU'S HIS FIANCEE,
SO SHE'S GOT DIBS!
- DON'T START WITH THAT
STUPID CLAIM AGAIN!
IT JUST MAKES THINGS
MORE COMPLICATED!
- SOMEONE SHOULD MAKE USE OF HIM
IF YOU'RE TOO SHY.
- WHAT DOES THAT MEAN?
- COME ON.
YOU HAVEN'T KISSED HIM TONIGHT.
- I KNOW. I'M JUST
NOT THAT HUNGRY, ALL RIGHT?
- ( screaming )
- ( sighing )
- I SAID NO KISSING!
- BUT ELFRIEDE DID.
- ONLY AFTER YOU DID IT FIRST!
THIS IS YOUR FAULT, KOUHEI!
YOU SHOULD BE A LOYAL SLAVE
INSTEAD OF TURNING YOUR NECK
INTO AN OPEN HOUSE!
- I'M NOBODY'S SLAVE, OKAY?
- Hazuki: OH...
- OH, DEAR. HE REALLY SAID IT.
- Ryuuhei: DIMWIT.
- WHAT?
YOU'RE GONNA PAY FOR THAT
YOU IDIOT!
- ( Kouhei screaming )
- Hazuki: STAND AT ATTENTION
- ( loud chattering )
- Hazuki: ARTE, I SAID STOP!
- Kouhei: TRUST ME
- YOU'RE NOT GONNA LIKE IT.
- Hazuki: DON'T ENCOURAGE HER!
- ( snoring )
- I'M TIRED BUT I CAN'T SLEEP.
IT'S THE DUMB MOON'S FAULT.
MY TEETH FEEL LIKE THEY'RE
GONNA EXPLODE!
- Hiromi: NO, I'M SERIOUS.
I JUST NEVER ASKED YOU BEFORE
BECAUSE I THOUGHT YOU'D SAY NO.
- SURE! I THINK
IT'S A SPECTACULAR IDEA.
- THEN LET'S DO IT!
LET GET MARRIED NEXT WEEK,
SEIJI,
AND THEN HAVE LITTLE
PSYCHIC BABIES.
HOORAY! NOW PINKY-SWEAR!
- HEY, CHECK IT OUT,
HIROMI THINKS HAIJI IS YOU.
- Seiji: THAT'S FUNNY.
- DOES THIS FEEL OKAY?
- OOH, YOU BETCHA.
THAT'S THE PERFECT
SPOT, RIGHT THERE!
- AND IT SEEMS LIKE THE MASSEUSE
AND HER CLIENT ARE
HAVING A BLAST.
- THAT CHILD.
DO YOU THINK SHE'LL ACTUALLY
BE ABLE TO GET ALONG HERE?
- IF IT'S ARTE YOU MEAN,
I'M SURE SHE'LL DO JUST FINE.
- I AGREE. SHE'LL HAVE HAZUKI,
AFTER ALL.
- Ryuuhei: YES. ARTE'S JUST LIKE
HAZUKI WAS AT A YOUNGER AGE.
- Kouhei: CAN'T SLEEP?
- I SLEPT TODAY.
- WANT TO PLAY A GAME THEN?
I'M UP FOR ANYTHING
BUT BOUNCY BALL.
- NO PLAYING.
WHEN YOU PLAY WITH SOMEONE,
THEY GO AWAY FOREVER.
BEING ALONE IS BETTER.
- DON'T SAY THAT.
- TEETH POUNDING.
CAN'T STAY IN BED.
WHAT IS THAT IDIOT UP TO NOW?
- TRAITOR!
- Kouhei: I KNOW HOW YOU FEEL,
BELIEVE IT OR NOT.
LONG TIME AGO,
I LOST SOMEONE TOO.
I WAS ABOUT YOUR AGE, ACTUALLY.
IT HURT SO BAD,
LIKE SOMEONE HAD SUCKED THE LIFE
RIGHT OUT OF MY CHEST.
I FELT SO ALONE.
I WASN'T, THOUGH.
I HAD GRANDPA AND SEIJI.
A FAMILY WHO CARED,
WHO WERE THERE FOR ME.
AND REALLY, THAT'S HOW
I GOT TO WHERE I AM TODAY.
'CAUSE I COULD
FALL BACK ON THEM.
YOU SHOULDN'T SAY
YOU DON'T NEED ANYONE.
'CAUSE THERE ARE SOME FRIENDS
WHO NEVER GO AWAY.
- OH, KOUHEI.
- YOU FEEL SO WARM.
- LIKE HAZUKI.
SHE'S A GOOD FRIEND.
WHEN SHE FIRST CAME
IT WAS HARD FOR HER, TOO.
SHE'D BEEN LOCKED
IN THAT CASTLE
AND DIDN'T KNOW HOW
TO TRUST PEOPLE.
SHE WAS A REAL HEADACHE.
OF COURSE,
SHE STILL IS SOMETIMES.
BUT SINCE WE'VE STUCK TOGETHER
THROUGH THE BAD STUFF,
I'VE REALLY GOTTEN TO KNOW HER,
AND SEEN THE GREAT STUFF TOO.
SHE'S GOT ONE
OF THE BIGGEST HEARTS I KNOW.
- Arte: YOU THINK SO?
- WHEN GRANDPA AND THE OTHERS
GOT HURT TRYING TO SAVE HER,
SHE FELT SO GUILTY.
SHE HATED THE IDEA
OF BEING RESPONSIBLE FOR THAT.
SHE'S JUST A YOUNG GIRL, BUT
SHE'S CARRIED THIS HUGE BURDEN
THINKING SHE'S A CURSE.
BUT. WHAT SHE DOESN'T GET
IS IT'S OUR CHOICE TO FIGHT.
SHE'S PART OF OUR FAMILY NOW,
AND WE LOVE HER.
IT WASN'T ABOUT HEROICS,
AND NOBODY'S GOING TO
HOLD IT OVER HER HEAD BUT HER.
WE JUST DID IT 'CAUSE
WE WANTED TO BE WITH HER
AND LAUGH WITH HER AGAIN.
IF YOU STAY HERE, ARTE.
THEN YOU'LL SEE.
HAZUKI!
- YOU'RE A TERRIBLE SLAVE.
BUT HONESTLY, I THINK I'M GLAD.
SHE IS CUTE.
- YOU HAVE TO
LOOK OUT FOR HER, HAZUKI.
- YEAH. WELL, SHE
IS MY HALF-SISTER, AFTER ALL.
WE'LL NEVER BE COMPLETELY
OUT OF DANGER, WILL WE?
- NO. I GUESS NOT.
- OTHER VAMPIRES ARE SURE
TO COME AFTER ME TOO,
TRYING TO GET MY POWER.
BUT I'M NOT WORRIED ABOUT IT.
'CAUSE I'VE GOT YOU GUYS.
AND I'VE GOT YOU MOST OF ALL,
DON'T I, KOUHEI?
- ( grunting )
- THINGS ARE OKAY, MOTHER.
I DON'T THINK YOU HAVE TO WORRY
ABOUT ME ANYMORE.
THANKS A LOT, KOUHEI.
- HAZUKI...
LISTEN. I SPENT A LONG TIME
WAITING FOR MY MOM, TOO.
AND I JUST...
I THINK IT'S TIME
THAT YOU LET GO
AND ADMIT THAT SHE'S GONE.
- YOU MEAN FOR GOOD?
YEAH, I UNDERSTAND.
SHE IS GONE.
I'VE KNOWN IT FOR A WHILE.
I ONLY...
YOU'RE RIGHT, KOUHEI...
WE HAVE EACH OTHER.
IT'S TIME TO MOVE ON.
- ( crying )
KOUHEI!
- HEY, WAIT A MINUTE.
YOU'VE FORGOTTEN SOMETHING.
RIGHT, HAZ?
THE FULL MOON'S OUT
AND YOU HAVEN'T HAD A
SINGLE DROP YET.
COME ON, YOU'RE STILL A VAMPIRE,
AREN'T YOU?
- ( laughing )
- ( exclaiming )
WHAT WAS THAT?
- TELL THE TRUTH, I'VE MATURED
A LITTLE
SINCE YOU'VE MET ME, RIGHT?
BUT ANYWAY. WELL, HERE I GO!
- IT SURE IS
A BEAUTIFUL MOON TONIGHT.
HEY, WHAT'RE YOU TRYING TO DO,
BITE THROUGH ME?
YOU'RE BITING TOO HARD!
- DON'T BE A BABY!
- WELL, CAN'T YOU JUST
TRY TO BE A LITTLE MORE GENTLE
WITH THOSE FANGS?
- NOT REALLY!
- ( Kouhei groaning )
- ( Hazuki laughing )
- WELL, GOODBYE, GIRLS.
HIKARU, KAORU.
- THANKS FOR HAVING US.
- WE HAD A LOT OF FUN.
THANK YOU.
- YOU BE CAREFUL
WHILE YOU'RE TRAVELING.
- DON'T WORRY, WE WILL.
- I'LL SEE YOU, KAORU.
COME BACK SOON, OKAY?
- ( meowing )
- SERIOUSLY THOUGH, KAORU,
I CAN'T BELIEVE YOU'RE GOING
OUTSIDE IN THAT GETUP.
- OH, LIKE YOU'RE ONE TO JUDGE.
CAT PAWS LOOK A HECK OF A LOT
BETTER THAN
THAT GHETTO COSTUME YOU
MADE FOR ARTE.
- WHAT'S "GHETTO"?
- DON'T LISTEN TO HER,
YOU LOOK GREAT!
- AM I GHETTO?
- DON'T YOU ANSWER HER!
- HERE, GIVE THIS
TO YOUR ELDERS, DEAR.
- ALL RIGHT. IT'S A NICE DAY.
I'LL WALK THEM TO THE STATION.
- CAN I COME TOO?
- WHAT?
- I WANT TO GO WITH YOU, HAZUKI.
-SURE, ARTE.
SOUNDS LIKE A GREAT IDEA!
- ( laughing )
NOT THAT'S HOW YOU END A SHOW!
- ( music playing )
- ( singing in Japanese )
- SHOW'S OVER!
NOW GO BUY SOME MERCHANDISE!
- All: CUE THE CREDITS!
- ( theme song playing )
- ( singing in Japanese )
- HOLD ON, BIG BROTHER!
WE MIGHT'VE WRAPPED
UP THE STORY,
BUT WE DIDN'T
WANT THE FUN TO END!
SO HERE'S ONE LAST QUESTION!
WHAT DO YOU DO WHEN
THE SHOW'S OVER,
BUT YOU'RE NOT READY
TO SAY GOODBYE?
FULL, FULL, FULL...
MOON!
THE ANSWER IS AN ENCORE, DUMMY!
NEXT TIME ON MOON PHASE,
IT'S THE REAL LAST EPISODE!
"UP AND DOWN, IN THE SUN,
FLOATING AWAY...
WHAT IS IT?"
YOU'LL HAVE TO WATCH
TO FIND OUT! GOODNIGHT!