- Hiromi: COUNT HEINRICH
VON KINKEL.
MEMBER OF ONE OF THE MOST
ILLUSTRIOUS NOBLE
FAMILIES IN EUROPE.
KNOWN AS "THE SORCERER
OF LIGHT AND SPACE."
WHATEVER THAT MEANS.
MASTER OF THE OCCULT AND SCHOLAR
OF ARCHAIC RELIGIOUS PRACTICES.
SO, BASICALLY THIS KINKEL GUY
IS THE HIGH MUCKETY-MUCK
OF ALL THINGS WEIRD,
BUT BEING INVITED
TO THIS EXHIBIT
MEANS GOOD THINGS FOR
THE MAGAZINE, RIGHT?
- WE'RE NOT HERE TO LOOK
AT HIS ARTWORK.
WE'RE HERE BECAUSE THE
COUNT WANTS A FAVOR.
HIS OFFICIAL REASON
FOR COMING TO JAPAN
IS TO CHECK ON THE EXHIBIT,
MAKE SURE EVERYTHING
GOES SMOOTHLY.
BUT HIS REAL REASON
IS TO TOUR SPIRITUAL HOT SPOTS
AND FURTHER HIS RESEARCH
ON THE OCCULT.
- WHAT'S A HOT SPOT?
- JUST SOMEPLACE
FREQUENTLY ACKNOWLEDGED
AS HAVING PARANORMAL ACTIVITY.
- I DON'T GET IT.
IF HE DOESN'T CARE
ABOUT THE EXHIBIT,
THEN WHY DID HE
AGREE TO OUR INTERVIEW?
- WELL, I BELIEVE THAT TIES INTO
THE FAVOR HE WANTED TO ASK US.
I'M PRETTY SURE HE'S GONNA
WANT YOU TO BE HIS GUIDE,
IN WHICH CASE YOU BETTER COME
BACK WITH SOME JUICY GOSSIP!
- ( she exclaims )
- ( he laughs )
- ( theme song playing )
- ( singing in Japanese )
- I HAVE FAILED YOU, MASTER.
FORGIVE ME.
I NEVER INTENDED FOR YOU
TO HAVE TO COME HERE YOURSELF.
- AND YET I FIND I MUST.
HOW UNFORTUNATE FOR US BOTH.
- I'M AFRAID MY MISTAKE
WAS IN WAITING.
I THOUGHT THAT WHEN
THE FULL MOON CAME
AND THE MISTRESS
SOUGHT HER KISS,
I WOULD BE ABLE
TO FOLLOW HER KI.
I WAS WRONG.
I KNOW SHE DRANK THAT NIGHT,
BUT SOMEHOW I WAS BLOCKED.
I COULDN'T SENSE HER WELL
ENOUGH TO FOLLOW.
AND I LOST THE CHANCE
TO BRING HER BACK. I'M SORRY.
- YOUR MISTAKE WAS
IN UNDERESTIMATING HER.
A MISTAKE I SEEM TO HAVE
MADE AS WELL.
I HAD HOPED SHE WOULD BE
CARELESS AND GIVE HERSELF AWAY.
BUT IT SEEMS
THAT'S NOT THE CASE.
EVEN I'VE BEEN UNABLE
TO SENSE HER LOCATION.
SO I CAN HARDLY FAULT YOU.
CAN I?
- WHERE ARE YOU GOING?
- TO THE GALLERY. I BELIEVE IT'S
TIME I MADE SOME NEW FRIENDS.
COULD HE TELL? COULD HE TELL
THAT I LIED TO HIM?
I LIED.
THAT MEANS I TRULY AM FREE.
BUT HE CAN'T FIND OUT. NOT YET.
IT'S STILL TOO DANGEROUS.
HE CAN'T FIND OUT THAT KOUHEI
MORIOKA IS THE VAMPIRE'S LOVER.
- WHERE DID IT GO?
AW, THIS IS GREAT! HEY, GRAMPS!
DO YOU KNOW WHERE MY GEAR IS?
I CAN'T FIND IT ANYWHERE!
- I CAN'T HEAR YOU!
- I SAID DO YOU KNOW
WHERE MY GEAR IS?
- YOU DIDN'T ACCIDENTALLY
SELL IT, DID YOU?
- OF COURSE NOT! IDIOT BOY.
ACTS LIKE I'M THE SENILE ONE.
I DIDN'T LOSE MY CAMERA.
- ( he sighs )
- I'M SORRY, GRAMPA.
IT'S JUST, I REALLY NEED
THIS GIG TO GO WELL,
AND WITHOUT
MY CAMERA THERE'S NO GIG.
- CALM DOWN.
YOU TAKE THINGS SO SERIOUSLY!
- WELL, WELL, WELL.
- ( crickets chirping )
- ( dog barking )
- I'M DOING WHAT YOU TOLD ME TO,
MAMA. I'M WAITING.
- HAZUKI?
WHAT ARE YOU DOING UP HERE?
IT'S DANGEROUS.
- GO AWAY, PLEASE.
- GO AWAY.
- A SLAVE SHOULD NEVER INTERRUPT
HIS MASTER WHEN
SHE'S CONCENTRATING.
- DEFINITELY NOT.
- FINE THEN, STAY UP HERE.
SEE IF I CARE.
FALL ASLEEP UP HERE AND GET
CAUGHT IN THE SUN, BY ALL MEANS.
DON'T EXPECT ME TO SCRAPE
YOU OFF THE ROOF WHEN YA DO.
- WHY NOT? YOU
SHOULD BE USED TO IT
WITH THE GRODY TOAST YOU MAKE.
- YEAH! GRODY.
- AH!
YOU'RE THE ONE WHO
STOLE MY WORK GEAR!
- SO, I SUPPOSE YOU HAVE
A GOOD REASON
FOR STEALING MY VERY EXPENSIVE
CAMERA EQUIPMENT.
- DON'T BE STUPID.
OF COURSE I DO.
MY MOTHER COULD BE COMING TO
FIND ME ANYTIME
NOW, YOU KNOW.
BUT, IF SHE'S LOST OR SHE'S IN
TROUBLE OR SOMETHING,
SHE MIGHT NEED ME TO HELP
HER WHEN SHE GETS CLOSER.
I HAVE TO BE READY.
- YEAH, ALL RIGHT.
JUST MAKE SURE YOU
ASK NEXT TIME, OKAY?
I NEED THAT STUFF FOR WORK.
- OOH!
- WHAT? WHAT IS IT?
WHOA! COME, ON.
COULDN'T THEY EVEN TAKE THE TIME
TO CLOSE THE FREAKIN' CURTAINS?
HEY! YOU'RE KIDDING ME!
THERE'S NO WAY THAT'S LEGAL.
IN FACT, I'M NOT EVEN
SURE THEY'RE OLD ENOUGH
TO KNOW IF
IT'S ILLEGAL.
WELL, THEY'RE ALL LUCKY.
I MEAN IT COULD'VE BEEN
SOME PERVERT UP HERE.
NO WAY! IS THAT... IT CAN'T BE.
IS THAT YOUR...
- ( he screams )
- MAMA!
- REALLY?
- I CAN'T BELIEVE IT! IT'S MAMA.
SHE CAME FOR ME JUST
LIKE SHE SAID SHE WOULD!
MAMA!
- HAZUKI! HAZUKI, WAIT!
- WAIT FOR ME!
- HEY! STOP!
- KOUHEI!
- TOO LATE. SHE'S GONE.
- ( Haiji whimpers )
- HAIJI? HAIJI!
HAIJI, WHO DID THIS TO YOU?
ARE YOU OKAY?
HAZUKI AND HER MOTHER,
DO YOU KNOW WHERE THEY WENT?
- KOUHEI!
YOU'RE WRONG.
I WASN'T THE ONE YOU SAW.
- THEN WHO WAS IT?
- NOT ME, BUT AN
ILLUSION OF MYSELF
USED TO LURE MY
DAUGHTER AWAY.
IT COULD NOT BE ME, KOUHEI,
NOT IN THAT FORM,
BECAUSE I NO LONGER EXIST.
- NO LONGER EXIST?
BUT WHAT ARE YOU TALKING ABOUT?
IF YOU NO LONGER EXIST,
THEN WHAT AM I LOOKING AT?
- A PHANTOM. AN ILLUSION.
MERELY A MESSENGER
LEFT FOR HAZUKI.
THE ONLY WAY MY TRUE SELF KNEW
TO LEAVE HER THOUGHTS BEHIND
WHEN SHE WAS
FORCED TO LEAVE THIS WORLD.
- WHAT DOES THAT MEAN?
"SHE WAS FORCED TO LEAVE."
COME ON, YOU DON'T MEAN
THAT SHE'S... THAT SHE'S DEAD.
THAT'S NOT WHAT YOU'RE SAYING,
RIGHT? HER MOM'S NOT DEAD!
- AND YET YOU TOLD HER THAT HER
MOTHER WAS COMING FOR HER.
YOU KEPT HER HOPE ALIVE.
DIDN'T YOU REALIZE HOW
CRUEL THAT WOULD BE?
HOW COULD YOU
MAKE THAT PROMISE?
- I COULDN'T TELL HER THE TRUTH.
I COULDN'T.
I'M AN ILLUSION, YES,
BUT ENDOWED WITH A MEMORY.
I COULDN'T BEAR TO
HURT THE LITTLE GIRL
THAT I REMEMBER
LOVING SO VERY MUCH.
PLEASE. TAKE GOOD CARE
OF MY DAUGHTER.
YOU'RE ALL THAT SHE HAS.
- WAIT, BEFORE YOU GO,
TELL ME HOW MY DAUGHTER'S
SHIKIGAMI MESSENGER
CAME TO BE IN YOUR POSSESSION
WHILE YOU WERE ALIVE.
- I'M SORRY. MY MEMORY
IS NOT THAT COMPLETE.
BUT I CAN SAY THIS.
THE ONE WHO HAS TAKEN MY
DAUGHTER MAY KNOW SOMETHING.
FIND HER.
AND PLEASE, HURRY.
- OKAY. WE'VE GOTTA SAVE HAZUKI.
THAT'S STRAIGHTFORWARD ENOUGH.
AW, MAN, I TOTALLY FORGOT.
WE DON'T EVEN KNOW
WHERE TO LOOK FOR HER!
DAMN! WHAT'RE WE GONNA DO?
THE TRAIL'S
PROBABLY COLD BY NOW!
- CALM DOWN. I MIGHT HAVE
AN IDEA WHERE SHE WAS TAKEN.
- ( he chuckles )
- ( wind howling )
- ( newspaper rustling )
- MASTER, I'M HUMBLED BY YOUR
POWER AS ALWAYS.
THAT YOU'VE ACCOMPLISHED
IN ONE NIGHT
WHAT I HAVE FAILED
TO ACHIEVE FOR SO LONG.
I WILL PREPARE
FOR OUR RETURN TO THE CASTLE
NOW THAT YOU HAVE
WHAT WE CAME HERE FOR.
- NOT QUITE YET, MY DEAR.
THERE IS SOME BUSINESS
YET TO TAKE CARE OF
BEFORE WE CAN RETURN
TO SCHWARTZ QUELLE.
SHORTLY, MISTRESS LUNA'S SLAVES
WILL BE COMING TO RESCUE HER.
IT IS MY INTENTION
TO ENSURE THEY NEVER LEAVE.
UNDERSTOOD?
THE GREAT MASTER MUST NEVER
BE TOLD OF THIS LITTLE MISHAP.
I WON'T RUN THE RISK OF HIM
EVER LEARNING MISTRESS LUNA
LEFT THE CONFINES
OF SCHWARTZ QUELLE.
SO, WE WILL ERASE ALL EVIDENCE
OF HER LIFE OUTSIDE ITS WALLS.
AND ELFRIEDE,
NO MISTAKES THIS TIME.
- NO.
- ( sinister laugh )
- THERE, I CAN FEEL IT.
THAT POWER. THERE! AGAIN!
I HAD MY SUSPICIONS FROM THE
PAPER, AND NOW THERE'S NO DOUBT.
THE CHILD IS BEING
HELD IN THAT BUILDING!
- ALL RIGHT, LET'S GO GET HER!
( he screams )
- HOLD IT!
- THE POWER I'M SENSING
IS NOT HAZUKI'S.
SOMEONE IN THAT BUILDING IS
RELEASING A DANGEROUS KI.
MUCH TOO DANGEROUS
FOR SOMEONE LIKE YOU.
WE'RE GOING TO HAVE
TO WAIT FOR SEIJI.
HOW LONG HAS IT BEEN
SINCE YOU CALLED HIM?
- A COUPLE OF MINUTES.
HE STILL WON'T ANSWER HIS PHONE.
AND THERE'S NO GUARANTEE HAIJI
WILL FIND HIM IN TIME, EITHER.
SO HOW LONG DO WE STAND HERE
WHILE HAZUKI'S LIFE
IS AT RISK, GRAMPS?
BEFORE YOU DECIDE
THAT I'M ENOUGH?
- KOUHEI. IT'S JUST
THAT YOU'RE...
- I KNOW! I KNOW WHAT I AM.
BELIEVE ME, I'VE
ALWAYS KNOWN, GRAMPA.
I MEAN, HOW COULD I FORGET?
REMEMBER THE BABY BIRD I FOUND
THAT DAY WHEN I WAS JUST A KID?
IT'D FALLEN OUT OF ITS
NEST OR SOMETHING,
AND IT WAS JUST
LAYING THERE, HELPLESS.
I WANTED TO SAVE IT,
MAKE IT BETTER.
DO SOMETHING.
BUT I DIDN'T KNOW HOW.
BROUGHT IT HOME AND FED IT,
WATCHED OVER IT DAY AND NIGHT.
I DID EVERYTHING IN MY POWER
TO MAKE THAT BIRD LIVE.
IT DIDN'T DO ANY GOOD.
THAT'S WHEN I REALIZED
WHAT "POWERLESS" MEANT
AND WHY MY FAMILY LOOKED AT ME
WITH SUCH PITY WHEN
THEY SAID IT.
BUT I'M TIRED, GRAMPA.
I'M TIRED OF BEING POWERLESS.
OF BEING USELESS.
AND I'M TIRED OF
WAITING AROUND
FOR SOMEBODY ELSE TO
GET ME OUT OF A JAM
WHILE I STAND THERE
AND DO NOTHING!
I'M GOING TO SAVE HAZUKI!
WITH OR WITHOUT YOU!
- IT SEEMS THE ENEMY HAS TAKEN
CONTROL OF THIS ENTIRE BUILDING.
WE DON'T KNOW WHAT HIS
PLANS FOR US ARE,
BUT I THINK WE CAN ASSUME HE
WON'T LET US THROUGH TOO EASILY.
BEST TO SPLIT UP.
LET'S HEAD FOR THE TOP FLOOR.
THAT'S WHERE
THEY'RE KEEPING THE GIRL.
I'LL TAKE THE ELEVATOR
AND MEET YOU THERE.
BE CAREFUL
GOING UP THE STAIRS, OKAY?
- HEY, WAIT A MINUTE!
WELL, I GUESS IT'S FOR THE BEST.
A MAN HIS AGE SHOULDN'T
CLIMB THAT MANY STAIRS, ANYWAY.
- YOU IDIOT!
- ( Kouhei gasps )
- I WILL RELEASE A POWERFUL KI,
WHICH THE ENEMY
WILL SENSE IMMEDIATELY!
YOU, HOWEVER,
RELEASE ONLY HOT AIR,
AND WILL BE ABLE TO SLIP
PAST HIM UNNOTICED. UNDERSTAND?
I'M PLAYING THE DECOY SO THAT
YOU CAN TAKE HIM BY SURPRISE!
I CAN'T BELIEVE I HAD
TO EXPLAIN ALL THAT.
DIDN'T YOU PLAY
VIDEO GAMES AS A KID?
TALISMANS TO WARD OFF SPELLS.
USE THEM.
WELL, SOMEONE HAS AN INTERESTING
TASTE IN ARTWORK. A BIT MORBID.
GO GYOU SHOUKOKU. GON!
- I SEE. SO IT WAS YOU
I SENSED AFTER ALL.
WELL, IF IT'S OUR FATE
THEN SO BE IT.
I CALL UPON THE GODS
OF THE FOUR SEAS,
AND INVOKE THE ANCIENT LAW!
REPEL THIS DEMON SPIRIT!
- THIS IS FREAKIN' RIDICULOUS.
UH, HELLO UP THERE? HI?
HEH-HEH. HEY, GUYS. SEEN ANY
GOOD ZOMBIE FLICKS LATELY?
- ( he screams )
SORRY, FELLAS,
I HATE TO HEX AND RUN.
I'M COMIN' FOR YOU, HAZUKI,
JUST HANG ON, OKAY?
I'M COMIN' FOR YOU!
- MAMA! I'M COMING!
I'M COMING FOR YOU!
- ( Kouhei screams )
- I WAS HOPING WE WOULD
MEET AGAIN, BOY.
- YOU'RE THAT GUY FROM
THE GERMAN CASTLE!
- VERY GOOD!
SO GLAD I MADE AN IMPRESSION.
BUT YOU KNOW, I'M FAIRLY CERTAIN
I CAN MAKE A BETTER ONE!
- MY LAST ONE.
- THAT'S ALL?
- ( Kouhei screams )
BECAUSE OF YOU, I FAILED TO
FULFILL MY DUTY
TO MISTRESS LUNA.
BECAUSE OF YOU
I NO LONGER HAVE A HUMAN FORM!
- COME ON.
C'MON, C'MON, C'MON!
- ( laughs )
- ( singing in Japanese )
- ( coughs )
- ELFRIEDE? WAIT A MINUTE,
WHAT THE HELL IS SHE DOING HERE?
- I SUMMON YOU!
GO GYOU HAKKI BI!
- GRANDPA!
THEY'RE FIGHTING! THAT MEANS
ELFRIEDE'S ONE OF THEM!
- GRANDPA!
- FLY! NOW!
- ( gasps )
GET AWAY, GET AWAY,
GET AWAY, GET AWAY!
- ( he laughs )
- ( he screams )
- NO! WHAT'S HAPPENING TO ME?
ELFRIEDE! WHAT IS THIS?
WHY AREN'T YOU DOING ANYTHING?
ELFRIEDE!
NO! YOU TRAITOR!
I SUPPOSE WE'RE LUCKY
YOUR IMMUNITY TO SPIRITS
ENABLES YOU TO DEFLECT
SHADOW MESSENGERS, KOUHEI.
AND LUCKY YOU DEFLECTED THEM IN
PRECISELY THE RIGHT DIRECTION.
THEN AGAIN, PERHAPS IT WASN'T
LUCK AT ALL. RIGHT, ELFRIEDE?
- YOU MEAN SHE DID THAT
ON PURPOSE?
YOU MEAN SHE'S ACTUALLY
ON OUR SIDE AFTER ALL?
- LET'S ASK HER, SHALL WE?
WAS IT MY IMAGINATION,
OR WERE YOU HOLDING BACK
WHEN YOU AND I WERE FIGHTING?
- WELL, ONLY A LITTLE.
- AW, MAN!
- ( he laughs )
- ELFRIEDE, WAIT A MINUTE.
WHAT ARE YOU DOING?
- I'M SORRY. BUT I'M AFRAID
I NEED THIS, KOUHEI.
AND ONLY YOUR BLOOD WILL DO.
LAST TIME IT WAS TO FREE
MYSELF FROM MY MASTER.
AND THIS TIME,
IT'S TO DEFEAT HIM.
- ( theme song plays )
- ( singing in Japanese )
- IT'S RIDDLE TIME,
MISTRESS LUNA.
HE WHO MAKES ME
DOESN'T WANT ME.
HE WHO BUYS ME DOESN'T USE ME.
HE WHO USES ME DOESN'T SEE ME.
WHAT AM I?
FULL, FULL, FULL MOON!
SORRY, MISTRESS, TIME'S UP.
THE ANSWER? A COFFIN.
- ( he laughs )
NEXT TIME ON MOON PHASE,
EPISODE 9: "SAVE ME
FROM THIS DREAM."