- ( grunts )
- NOT TOO BAD!
- OH, WELL THAT'S JUST BECAUSE
YOUR ATTACKS ARE SO OBVIOUS.
- MY ATTACKS ARE OBVIOUS, HUH?
FINE. LET'S SEE YOU BLOCK THIS.
( exclaiming )
HOW OBVIOUS IS THIS?
- THAT WAS TOTALLY UNCALLED FOR.
- WELL, I GUESS THAT'S JUST
THE FRUIT OF MY DAILY DILIGENCE.
- MEET THE FRUIT JUICER!
( grunts )
- SWINGING A STICK AROUND
WITH NO TECHNIQUE IS NO
WAY TO WIN A SWORD FIGHT.
UNCALLED FOR...
- YOU SEE? TALENT WILL
ALWAYS BEAT DILIGENCE.
- YOU JUST GOT LUCKY,
DEMON FREAK!
- ( unintelligible chatter )
- ( theme song playing )
- ( singing in Japanese )
- Haiji: STOP FIGHTING,
YOU BIG BABIES!
GOOD. KAORU WAS STARTING
TO GET A HEADACHE.
- OH, WE WEREN'T FIGHTING.
UH, WE WERE JUST PRETENDING.
YEAH, THAT'S IT.
WE WERE PLAYING SHRINE MAIDEN
BEATS UP THE DEMON INTERLOPER.
- THAT IS SO NOT WHAT
WE WERE PLAYING!
IT WAS VAMPIRE THROWS
DOWN ON SHORT UGLY GIRL.
- DID YOU SAY "UGLY"?
- NO. ACTUALLY I SAID
SHORT AND UGLY.
- UM, GIRLS?
( clears throat )
KAORU SAYS YOU SHOULD
PROBABLY TAKE A LOOK
BEHIND YOU RIGHT ABOUT NOW.
- Both: OH, MASTER YAYOI.
- YAHOO! HI-HO!
I'LL SEE YOU SOON!
- Yayoi: IT'S BEEN EIGHT MONTHS
SINCE YOU CAME HERE
SEEKING SHELTER.
DID YOU KNOW THAT?
TELL ME, IN THOSE EIGHT MONTHS,
DO YOU FEEL YOU'VE BEEN
FULFILLING YOUR DUTIES?
THE CONDITION OF YOUR
SANCTUARY WAS THAT YOU
LOOK AFTER AND MAINTAIN THE
MIDO FAMILY'S FUTTSU SHRINE.
I DON'T REMEMBER ANY STIPULATION
ABOUT FIGHTING IN FRONT OF IT.
- THIS IS YOUR FAULT, YOU KNOW.
- HEY, YOU STARTED IT.
- NUH-UH. STUPID DEMON GIRL.
- WHATEVER. YOU UGLY...
- ARE YOU QUITE FINISHED?
- Girls: SORRY, MASTER.
- I DON'T SEE WHY
I GOT YELLED AT.
YOU'RE THE ONE WHO WANTED
TO HAVE A SWORD MATCH.
TROUBLEMAKER.
- THAT'S RIGHT.
- WHAT?
- WE NEVER FIGURED OUT WHO WAS
THE WINNER OF THE MATCH, DID WE?
WE GOT INTERRUPTED BEFORE WE
COULD SEE WHO WAS STRONGEST.
- YOU'RE GONNA FIGHT AGAIN?
- AND GET YELLED AT BY THE
MASTER AGAIN? NO THANKS!
- THAT'S WHY WE HAVE
TO MAKE IT SOMETHING
WE WON'T GET IN TROUBLE FOR.
- SOMETHING MASTER YAYOI
WOULD WANT US TO DO ANYWAY.
FINE, THEN.
YOUR CHALLENGE IS ACCEPTED.
- UM. SISTER...
- GOOD. THEN WE'LL MAKE IT
BEST 2 OUT OF 3.
ROUND ONE! MOPPING THE FLOORS!
GIVE IT YOUR BEST SHOT,
DEMON GIRL!
- BRING IT, ZIT-FACE!
I'M A MOPPING GOD!
- YOU WISH!
- LET'S GO, MOPPERS.
LET'S GO.
- Hazuki: ROUND TWO!
REPAPERING THE SCREEN DOORS!
- Hikaru: ROUND THREE!
POLISHING THE PILLARS!
- I GUESS MY SCOLDING
REALLY SANK IN.
- Hikaru: HAZUKI, MASTER.
- Hazuki: THAT WAS LAME.
SAY IT AGAIN,
BUT THIS TIME SAY
IT WITH GUSTO!
- HAZUKI, MASTER!
- GOOD! MUCH BETTER.
- ( groans )
THIS IS SO HUMILIATING!
- THEN MAYBE YOU SHOULD HAVE
CLEANED FASTER. LOSER.
- SO, KAORU. DO I WANT
TO KNOW? OR DON'T I?
- HIKARU LOST THE
CLEANING CONTEST
SO SHE HAS TO CALL MY
MASTER "MASTER," MASTER!
- UH-HUH.
- WATCH THE ROCK!
ARE YOU ALL RIGHT?
- JUST OLD, DEAR.
- HERE. LET ME TAKE CARE
OF THIS FOR YOU, GRANDMOTHER.
- SUCH A SWEET CHILD.
- OH! IT'S NOTHING.
I MEAN, IT'S THE LEAST I CAN DO
WHEN YOU AND MASTER YAYOI
ARE PUTTING UP WITH ME.
I OWE YOU SO MUCH.
- OH, YOU OWE US NOTHING,
MY DEAR. YOU'RE A PLEASURE.
- YOU DON'T HAVE TO SAY THAT,
GRANDMOTHER. I'M A BRAT.
- REALLY? AND I WAS GOING TO
TELL YOU OUR MIDO FAMILY SECRET.
- YEAH?
- Hikaru: WHAT IS THIS,
A NATURE HIKE?
- JUST SHUT UP.
WE'RE ALMOST THERE, I THINK.
- ( gasping )
- IT LOOKS LIKE A FAIRYTALE.
- IT'S HARD TO BELIEVE THIS
PLACE IS EVEN REAL, ISN'T IT?
- YEAH, I KNOW. IT'S INCREDIBLE.
IT'S LIKE A PAINTING.
- YEAH, OR LIKE A DREAM OR
SOMETHING. IT'S GREAT, HUH?
HEY, HOLD ON!
ISN'T THERE SOMETHING ELSE
YOU'RE SUPPOSED TO SAY?
- OH, RIGHT.
HAZUKI MASTER, MASTER, MASTER.
- HEY, LOOK.
- ( giggling )
- HEY. WE SHOULD COME BACK
HERE AGAIN TOMORROW.
- OKAY!
- YEAH!
- I JUST WISH THAT...
I WISH KOUHEI WAS HERE.
- I'M SORRY. WHAT?
- OH, NOTHING!
IT WAS SILLY.
- ( chattering )
- IT'S THE PRETTIEST
PLACE I'VE EVER SEEN!
- THERE WERE FLOWERS EVERYWHERE!
- SO I GOT YOU THESE.
THEY'RE FROM THIS AMAZING PLACE
THAT GRANDMOTHER TOLD ME ABOUT.
I GOTTA KEEP YOUR ALTAR LOOKING
SPIFFY, YOU KNOW?
I MISS YOU, GRANDPA.
ELFRIEDE.
- NOW BE CAREFUL. THE PACK'S
A LITTLE HEAVY THIS MONTH.
- I'LL BE OKAY.
THANKS, GRANDMOTHER.
- YOU LOOK GOOD ENOUGH TO SPREAD
ON CRACKERS, MASTER.
- THANKS, HAIJI.
- AND LIT UP
LIKE A LANTERN, TOO.
EXCITED ABOUT SEEING YOUR
GOOD FRIEND, I SUPPOSE.
- OH. YEAH, I GUESS SO.
I MEAN, I KNOW I CAN'T BE
WITH HIM WHILE HE'S IN TRAINING.
AND I WOULDN'T BOTHER HIM IF IT
WASN'T FOR THE FULL MOON THING,
BUT SINCE IT'S ONLY ONCE A MONTH
I GUESS IT'S OKAY.
- COME ON, HAZUKI, YOU KNOW
YOU'RE DYING TO SEE HIM.
JUST SAY IT.
- HAZUKI WHAT?
- WAIT, YOU MEAN...
- DID I HEAR A "MASTER"
AFTER THAT?
- HEY, THAT WAS DAYS AGO.
GET OVER YOURSELF!
- A DEAL IS A DEAL,
DEAL-BREAKER!
BYE!
- HAVE A GOOD TIME NOW, DEAR.
- SHE'S REALLY
DIFFERENT, ISN'T SHE,
THAN SHE WAS WHEN
SHE GOT HERE.
- IT'S BEEN EIGHT MONTHS SINCE
THEY SHOWED UP LOOKING FOR
A SAFE PLACE TO HIDE.
SHE'S HAD SOME TIME TO ABSORB
HER LOSSES AND MOVE ON.
- IT WAS HARD
SEEING HER SO DEPRESSED.
- IT WAS. I'M JUST GLAD SHE
HAD YOU TWO GIRLS AROUND.
WHO KNOWS WHERE SHE WOULD BE
IF IT WASN'T FOR YOU?
I DO BELIEVE IT WAS YOU WHO
BROUGHT HER BACK TO LIFE.
- BUT, NOW THAT SHE'S HAPPY,
DO YOU THINK WE'RE GONNA
BE ENEMIES AGAIN?
- NO.
- WHAT AM I GETTING SAD ABOUT?
JUST 'CAUSE I'M
LEAVING THE SHRINE?
DON'T I REMEMBER WHO
I'M GOING TO SEE? KOUHEI!
( panting )
( sighs )
FULL, FULL, FULL MOON!
( gasps )
KOUHEI?
THIS IS THE SECOND MONTH
IN A ROW HE HASN'T BEEN HERE.
I KNOW HE CAN'T STAY
IN HERE ALL THE TIME,
BUT DIDN'T HE KNOW
I WAS COMING?
WAIT A MINUTE.
I'M NOT JUST GONNA SIT HERE.
I'M GONNA GO FIND HIM.
THERE YOU ARE.
I'VE BEEN WALKING FOREVER.
I'M PRETTY SURE THIS
IS WHERE I SAW HIM.
GEEZ! WHAT'S HE DOING OUT
SO FAR, ANYWAY?
PROBABLY LOST. STUPID KOUHEI!
WHERE ARE YOU?
- ( rustling )
- IS THAT HIM?
WAIT. THIS ENERGY...
WHOEVER IT IS,
IT'S DEFINITELY NOT KOUHEI.
( gasps )
- ( growling )
( roaring )
- NO! STAY AWAY FROM ME!
( screams )
OH, MAN! WHY DID IT HAVE TO BE
A BLOB MONSTER?
I HATE BLOB MONSTERS!
OH, GREAT! IT'S A SPIRIT
SUCKER. THIS IS SO NOT GOOD.
KOUHEI, WHERE ARE YOU?
I HARDLY HAVE ANY POWER LEFT.
I NEED BLOOD! HOW AM I
SUPPOSED TO FIGHT THIS THING?
- ( roaring )
- I HATE THIS. IT'S LIKE...
IT'S LIKE THAT NIGHT
WHEN ALL WE COULD DO WAS RUN.
WE WERE POWERLESS TO FIGHT BACK.
BUT AT LEAST KOUHEI
WAS WITH ME.
NOW... NOW I'M ALL ALONE.
WHERE ARE YOU? I NEED YOU.
( screaming )
NO, ALL OF KOUHEI'S THINGS!
- Kouhei: HAZUKI? HAZUKI.
- KOUHEI! IT'S YOU.
- YEAH, OF COURSE IT'S ME.
WHO DO YOU THINK IT WAS, GOOF?
THAT'S A TIGHT GRIP
YOU MUST'VE REALLY MISSED ME.
I'M HERE NOW.
- LIKE I EVEN CARE. I'M
ONLY HERE FOR YOUR BLOOD.
HAS IT BEEN A WHILE?
I DIDN'T EVEN NOTICE!
SO DON'T GO THINKING
I'M LONELY WITHOUT YOU.
- WELL, I WAS LONELY.
- KOUHEI?
UM, NOW THAT YOU'RE HERE,
I WAS WONDERING,
CAN I KISS YOU?
- YOU COULD. EXCEPT...
- WHAT, DO YOU NOT WANT ME TO?
- NO. IT'S JUST THAT THIS TIME
I THINK I'D LIKE TO KISS YOU,
IF YOU DON'T MIND.
( evil laughter )
- ( screaming )
- KOUHEI!
- COME ON.
DON'T YOU WANNA KISS ME, HAZUKI?
YEAH.
HAZUKI!
- ( exclaims in fear )
IT'S GONNA SUCK OUT MY SPIRIT!
- ( laughing )
- KOUHEI, WHERE ARE YOU?
YOU'RE SUPPOSED TO BE HERE!
I NEED YOU.
YOU SHOULD NEVER HAVE
LEFT ME ALONE.
KOUHEI, NO!
- Kouhei: DID YOU CALL ME?
- ( monster snarling )
- SO, WHAT'S UP?
- IS... IS IT REALLY YOU NOW?
- WELL, OF COURSE IT'S ME, BRAT.
WHAT ARE YOU DOING HERE, ANYWAY?
- WHAT DO YOU MEAN
WHAT AM I DOING?
ISN'T IT A LITTLE OBVIOUS?
WAIT! KOUHEI CAN'T SEE SPIRITS.
HE DOESN'T KNOW!
- OH, YEAH. YOU MEAN
YOUR LITTLE BUDDY THERE.
- ( screams )
- THESE THINGS AREN'T VERY
STRONG. I CAN HANDLE THIS.
THAT WHICH IS NOT
OF THIS WORLD,
BRINGER OF DARKNESS AND
CREATURE OF THE SHADOWS.
- IS KOUHEI DOING
AN INCANTATION?
- IN THE REALM OF THE LIVING
HERE YOU WILL DO NO MORE HARM.
RETURN NOW FROM WHENCE YOU CAME!
I COMMAND YOU, FOUL DEMON!
- ( monster screaming )
- ( explosion )
- VERY WELL DONE, KOUHEI.
- YES. I'D SAY HE PASSED THE
TEST WITH FLYING COLORS.
THE YOUNG MAN'S MADE REMARKABLE
STRIDES THESE LAST FEW MONTHS.
ESPECIALLY WHEN YOU CONSIDER
HOW LITTLE HE KNEW BEFORE.
IMPRESSIVE.
- SO, DO YOU THINK
HE WAS PROTECTING HER?
- UH-HUH. HAZUKI SHOULD
BE WITH HIM BY NOW.
IS THAT WHY YOU CAME, HIKARU,
TO SEE SHE GOT THERE SAFELY?
- KOUHEI IS KAORU'S FIANCEE,
NOT HAZUKI'S STUPID SLAVE.
IT'S MY SISTER HE SHOULD
BE WORRYING ABOUT.
- YOU OKAY?
- KOUHEI, WHERE DID YOU
LEARN TO DO THAT?
YOU'VE NEVER EVEN BEEN
ABLE TO SEE SPIRITS.
IS THIS ALL BECAUSE
OF YOUR TRAINING?
YOU MUST BE WORKING HARD.
- I GUESS. I'M DOING EVERYTHING
SENSEI YAYOI TOLD ME TO.
BUT IF YOU WANNA
KNOW THE TRUTH,
THAT'S THE FIRST
TIME I'VE BEEN ABLE TO
PULL OFF SOMETHING LIKE THAT.
- THE FIRST TIME?
- ( laughs )
- THANK YOU, KOUHEI.
- HEY, WHAT'S THAT DOPEY
LOOK ABOUT, SHORT STUFF?
ARE YOU OVERWHELMED
BY MY RUGGED GOOD LOOKS?
- MAYBE IT WAS THE STENCH.
YOU SMELL LIKE A PIG.
- I'M LIVING IN A FREAKING TREE!
- EXCUSES, EXCUSES,
YOU BIG OINKER!
- OH, YEAH? YOU VAMPIRE!
- WHAT, ARE YOU RETARDED?
"YOU VAMPIRE"? LIKE
THAT'S EVEN AN INSULT!
- IF ALL VAMPIRES ARE LIKE YOU,
THEN IT IS AN INSULT!
- WHAT DO YOU KNOW,
YOU BIG JERK?
- I KNOW THAT YOU
ARE REALLY STUPID.
- Aruto: JEDA?
- MISTRESS ARTE. GOOD EVENING.
- THIS PLACE, IT'S FILTHY.
- Vargas: YOU COULD
HAVE AT LEAST CLEANED
BEFORE WE ARRIVED, JEDA.
- Jeda: I'VE NEVER REALLY BEEN
BOTHERED BY FILTH.
- SO? ANY MORE CLUES?
- NOTHING SUBSTANTIAL.
- NOTHING? WHAT HAVE
YOU BEEN DOING?
- I DID FIND THIS PLACE,
OF COURSE.
YOUR GRATITUDE IS
OVERWHELMING, VARGAS.
- THERE'S NOTHING HERE.
IT'S USELESS.
- MISTRESS ARTE.
I'M NOT POSITIVE IT'S HER,
BUT THERE'S A PLACE THAT'S
EMITTING STRANGE WAVES.
I THINK IT MIGHT BE
WORTH INVESTIGATING.
MISTRESS?
- I DON'T REALLY CARE. I CAME
HERE BECAUSE I WAS TOLD TO.
I LOOK FOR HER
BECAUSE I WAS TOLD TO.
I HAVE NO DESIRE TO MEET HER.
WHY SHOULD I? I HATE HER.
I HATE HER.
- ( theme song playing )
- ( singing in Japanese )
- Kouhei: HAZUKI,
IT'S RIDDLE TIME! READY?
FULL, FULL, FULL, MOON!
RIDDLE, RIDDLE, RIDDLE, RIDDLE,
RIDDLE, RIDDLE, RIDDLE, RIDDLE!
OKAY. NEXT TIME ON
MOON PHASE, EPISODE 19,
"DAY ON THE MOUNTAIN, MONKEY IN
THE SPA, THE CAT'S WHISKERS...
AND WHO ARE YOU?"
OH, I'M SORRY.
IS THAT NOT WHAT
"RIDDLE TIME" MEANS?
I HAVEN'T BEEN PAYING ATTENTION.