- Hazuki: MAMA?
- Woman: WHAT IS IT, SWEETHEART?
- Hazuki: UM, I KNOW I'M NOT
A LITTLE KID ANYMORE,
BUT CAN I PUT MY HEAD
IN YOUR LAP? AND SLEEP?
MAMA, I LOVE YOU.
I'M GLAD YOU'RE BACK.
- ( lightning bolt )
- I'M SO HAPPY.
- Kinkel: CLING TO YOUR
DREAMS, CHILD.
THEY ARE MY GIFT TO YOU,
WELCOMING YOU BACK TO THE FOLD.
I WENT TO GREAT PAINS
TO FIND YOU,
AND SOON I WILL HAVE MY REWARD
AS YOU CEASE TO BE HAZUKI
AND BECOME MISTRESS LUNA.
- Elfriede: COUNT KINKEL,
MY MASTER.
- WHAT IS IT, ELFRIEDE?
I PERMIT YOU TO SPEAK.
- FORGIVE MY
INTERRUPTION, MASTER.
BUT OUR VIGO HAS
BEEN DESTROYED.
- HOW DID THIS HAPPEN?
- THERE WERE MORE
CONJURORS THAN EXPECTED.
THEY CAUGHT US BOTH OFF GUARD.
I'M COUNTERING THEIR
ATTACK AS WE SPEAK,
BUT ONE OF THEM MAY BE
HEADING TO YOUR FLOOR.
PLEASE BE CAREFUL, MY MASTER.
- DON'T WORRY ABOUT ME, SLAVE.
GOOD NEWS, CHILD.
I NEED MORE TIME BEFORE
YOU AWAKE AS MISTRESS LUNA.
YOU MAY ENJOY YOUR DREAMS
A LITTLE LONGER.
- ( thunder rumbling )
- ( theme song playing )
- ( singing in Japanese )
- Kouhei: RIGHT ON SCHEDULE,
ELFRIEDE. JUST LIKE YOU SAID.
- Elfriede: I MUST
DESTROY COUNT KINKEL.
YOU MAY HELP ME, IF YOU DESIRE.
- DESTROY HIM? I THOUGHT YOU
TWO WERE ON THE SAME SIDE.
- NOT QUITE.
- SO MUCH FOR
GETTING USED TO THIS.
WHAT'S WRONG WITH YOU VAMPIRES,
DON'T YOU HAVE ANY MANNERS?
- IT WAS JUST A LITTLE KISS.
- TELL THAT TO THE
HOLES IN MY NECK!
YOU'VE GOTTA WARN ME
WHEN YOU DO THAT!
- I DON'T UNDERSTAND.
YOUR FANGS ARE STILL WET
WITH KOUHEI'S BLOOD.
OBVIOUSLY YOU EMBRACE
WHAT YOU ARE.
- WHY YOU WOULD WANT TO DESTROY
ONE OF YOUR OWN KIND?
- I'M A VAMPIRE, YES.
BUT IT HASN'T ALWAYS BEEN
THIS WAY FOR ME.
I'M NOT ONE OF THE BLUE BLOOD,
BORN UNDER VAMPIRE LINEAGE.
THERE WAS A TIME WHEN I WAS
PURELY HUMAN, JUST LIKE YOU.
I AM A LUDO, A HUMAN VICTIM
WHO WAS CHOSEN
TO BE TURNED VAMPIRE BY
HER MASTER'S KISS.
VAMPIRES LIKE ME ARE BOUND
TO THE ONES WHO BITE US.
WE ARE THEIR SLAVES.
POWERLESS TO DISOBEY,
CHAINED TO THEIR COMMANDS.
THEIR REIGN OVER OUR MINDS
IS SO FAR REACHING,
WE'RE NOT EVEN CAPABLE
OF TELLING THEM LIES.
COUNT KINKEL HAS BEEN MY MASTER,
THE ONE I'VE OBEYED FOR FAR
TOO LONG. BUT NOT ANYMORE.
EVERYTHING'S CHANGED NOW THAT
KOUHEI'S COME INTO THE PICTURE.
- ( gasps )
- YOU ARE DIFFERENT
THAN MOST, KOUHEI.
OUR BITES HAVE NO
EFFECT ON YOU.
SURELY YOU MUST'VE REALIZED THAT
FROM YOUR EXPERIENCES
WITH MISTRESS LUNA.
SHE DRINKS YOUR BLOOD, BUT YOU
HAVE NOT BECOME HER SLAVE.
BUT THERE'S ANOTHER
CONSEQUENCE OF YOUR
SUPERNATURAL ESTRANGEMENT THAT
MAKES YOU IMPORTANT TO ME.
JUST AS YOU CANNOT
BECOME A SLAVE,
ANY LUDO WHO TASTES
YOUR BLOOD IS RELEASED
FROM HER MASTER'S POWER AS WELL.
- YOU MEAN KOUHEI'S MADE YOU
FREE NOW THE WAY HAZUKI IS?
- I'D HEARD OF THIS BEFORE.
THE VAMPIRE'S LOVER.
BUT ONLY AS LEGEND, A STORY
LUDO TELL THEMSELVES
TO HELP THEM FALL ASLEEP.
BUT I'VE EXPERIENCED
IT MYSELF NOW...
- AND I KNOW HE IS REAL.
- COMPELLING, INDEED.
- I HAVE PLACED MY
LIPS ON HIM TWICE
SINCE I DISCOVERED WHAT
HE TRULY WAS.
THE FIRST WAS TO
MAKE MYSELF FREE.
BUT TONIGHT I DRANK HIS BLOOD TO
GIVE MYSELF STRENGTH FOR BATTLE.
- HMM. SO WE HAVE COME ON
THREE SEPARATE PATHS,
BUT THEY ALL LEAD TO
THE SAME PLACE.
ELFRIEDE, YOU'RE HERE TO FIGHT,
TO ENSURE YOUR NEW FREEDOM.
- AND KOUHEI, YOU'VE COME
TO SAVE A LITTLE GIRL.
- AND YOU?
- I'VE COME TO ASK
THE COUNT A QUESTION
I'VE HAD FOR OVER TEN YEARS NOW.
- THEN, GOOD THING I HAVE THIS.
- YOU CAN DO THIS, KOUHEI.
- Kinkel: SO YOU'RE THE ONE
WHO DESTROYED VIGO.
- IS THAT YOU, COUNT?
( gasps )
- NICE TRAP. YOU'RE VERY NIMBLE
FOR A WRINKLED, OLD MAN.
- FORGIVE THE RUDE GREETING.
BUT I HAVE A QUESTION AND I WANT
TO MAKE SURE YOU'RE LISTENING.
- WELL, I'M ALL EARS.
- CHIZURU MIDO.
DOES THAT NAME RING A BELL?
- ( laughs )
I HOPED YOU WERE GOING TO ASK
ME SOMETHING INTERESTING.
- ANSWER ME! DO YOU KNOW HER?
- THERE IS NOTHING I DETEST MORE
THAN BEING REMINDED
OF UNPLEASANT THINGS.
- JUST MY LUCK.
NO LIGHTS HERE EITHER.
THE WHOLE CIRCUIT
MUST BE TRIPPED.
HAZUKI, ARE YOU IN HERE?
CAN YOU HEAR ME?
ELFRIEDE SAID SOMETHING
ABOUT A BACK BEDROOM.
( exclaims )
NEXT TIME I AM DEFINITELY
BRINGING A FLASHLIGHT.
HUH?
HAZUKI!
OH, COME ON, WHAT THE HELL?
OH. PLEASE. NO! IT'S JUST LIKE
THE CASTLE ALL OVER AGAIN!
- ( laughing )
NOW. LET'S SEE HOW WELL
YOU CAN DEFEND, OLD MAN.
- CHIZURU IS MY DAUGHTER
AND SHE WAS SOMEHOW INVOLVED
WITH YOUR KIND!
TELL ME WHAT YOU KNOW!
- ( laughs )
YOU MUST BE HARD OF HEARING!
I TOLD YOU I DON'T WANT
TO REMEMBER HER!
- ( groaning )
- WHAT'S THE MATTER?
HAVE I BEEN TOO ROUGH ON
YOUR AGED AND FRAGILE BONES?
I HOPE YOU'RE NOT QUITTING
BEFORE I'VE HAD ANY FUN.
THAT'S MORE LIKE IT. I'M IN
THE MOOD FOR A GOOD RACE.
IT'S TOO BAD YOU'VE JUST
COME TO A DEAD END.
I SEE. THIS ISN'T CHASE.
IT'S HIDE AND SEEK.
- I SUMMON YOU, ARMADEL.
- ELFRIEDE, I SHOULD'VE KNOWN.
- ( grunts )
DAMN IT!
GRAMPA'S DOIN' ALL HE CAN.
EVEN ELFRIEDE'S PITCHING IN!
AND JUST LOOK AT ME.
I'M ALL ALONE.
I DON'T EVEN HAVE THE POWER TO
BREAK SOME STUPID VINES!
( grunting ) DAMN IT!
DAMN! DAMN!
( screaming )
I'M NOT QUITTING! I'M GETTING
YOU OUT, YOU HEAR ME?
I'M NOT GONNA BE
WORTHLESS EVER AGAIN!
- THIS CERTAINLY EXPLAINS YOUR
INCOMPETENCE WITH THE GIRL.
- BEHIND YOU IS A
FISSURE IN SPACE TIME,
CUT BY THE GOD OF SORCERY.
- YOU DARE TAKE ALLEGIANCE WITH
HUMANS, AND DEFY YOUR MASTER?
( Kinkel laughing )
WHAT AN INTERESTING DEVELOPMENT.
ETERNAL LIFE CAN BE
SO BORING, AT TIMES.
AFTER A WHILE
YOU'VE SEEN IT ALL.
BUT THIS!
THIS IS ENTIRELY NEW.
HOW DID THE SLAVE
BREAK HER CHAINS?
NOW THAT IS A REAL ENIGMA
WORTH PONDERING.
THIS IS YOUR FINAL CHANCE
TO CO-OPERATE, COUNT.
TELL ME WHAT HAPPENED
TO MY DAUGHTER
OR YOU'LL MEET YOUR FATE
WITH NO SYMPATHY FROM ME.
- ( laughing )
YOU HONESTLY THINK YOU'RE IN A
POSITION TO MAKE DEMANDS?
THAT I'M AFRAID OF A LITTLE
PINPRICK IN SPACE?
- HE WON'T HELP YOU.
- DO AS YOU'VE PLANNED.
- ( screaming )
- I'M SEALING IT.
- DO YOU REALLY THINK
WE'VE DEFEATED HIM?
- NO ONE COULD EVER ESCAPE THAT
VACUUM, NOT EVEN THE COUNT.
- THEN YOU'VE
REALIZED YOUR DREAM.
YOU ARE PERMANENTLY FREE.
- SO IT WOULD SEEM,
AND IT'S ALL THANKS TO HIM.
- ALL THANKS TO WHOM?
- THAT'S AN ODD THING
FOR YOU TO ASK.
- ELFRIEDE, GET AWAY!
- I DON'T UNDERSTAND.
- QUIET.
- I'M DISAPPOINTED IN YOU,
MY LITTLE SLAVE.
HAVE YOU FORGOTTEN
WHAT I'M CAPABLE OF?
NOW TELL ME WHO
YOU MEANT BY "HIM"?
- ( grunting )
I'M NOT QUITTING! NEVER!
- Woman: SEE THE MOON? ONCE
IT'S FREE FROM THE CLOUDS,
YOU'LL EMERGE TOO.
YOU'LL BE LUNA AGAIN.
- Hazuki: ME? LUNA?
- YES, THAT'S WHO YOU ACTUALLY
ARE, MY SWEET DAUGHTER.
HAZUKI'S JUST A MADE UP PERSON.
YOU'VE BEEN VERY GOOD AT
PRETENDING, BUT PLAYTIME'S OVER.
YOUR REAL NAME IS LUNA,
AND I'M HAPPY YOU'LL
BE HER AGAIN SOON.
- Kouhei: HAZUKI!
JUST. HOLD ON. PLEASE!
- I KNOW THAT VOICE.
I'VE HEARD IT BEFORE.
HE CALLS ME HAZUKI.
IS THAT WHO I AM?
- Seiji: HIROMI AND
THE EDITOR-IN-CHIEF
STILL HAVEN'T SHOWN UP YET?
- Editor: NAH. HAVEN'T HEARD
A PEEP FROM THEM
SINCE THEY WENT OUT ON
SOME STORY ASSIGNMENT.
AH, YEAH, YOU HAD AN APPOINTMENT
WITH HER, DIDN'T YOU?
SORRY, MAN, WE SHOULD
HAVE CALLED.
- YOU WOULDN'T HAVE
REACHED ME, ANYWAY.
I WAS WORKING ON MY MANUSCRIPT
IN THE LIBRARY BASEMENT.
MY CELL DOESN'T WORK
DOWN THERE.
- Haiji: THERE YOU ARE!
- HAIJI, WHAT'RE YOU DOING HERE?
YOU'RE SOAKED.
- BIG TROUBLE!
- PSYCHIC HOLOGRAMS!
- THAT'S RIGHT, OLD MAN.
- DROP HER!
WHERE ARE YOU, COUNT?
- RIGHT HERE!
- ( groans )
- YOUR RECOGNITION OF
TECHNIQUES IS IMPRESSIVE.
BY USING MY POWERS
I CAN BEND LIGHT,
CHANGING THE WAY IT REFRACTS TO
CREATE ANY APPEARANCE I CHOOSE.
AN OPTICAL ILLUSION.
AND ONCE I MASTERED THE BASICS,
I LEARNED TO TAKE IT FURTHER.
TWO IMAGES, BUT WHICH IS REAL?
MAYBE NEITHER IS.
YOU WON'T KNOW UNTIL THERE'S
A BOOT AT YOUR THROAT.
SUFFICE TO SAY HER LAST ATTACK
WAS WAY OFF THE MARK.
- DON'T HURT HER.
- BUT I HAVE TO FIND OUT HOW
THIS SLAVE BETRAYED ME.
TELL ME ELDER,
YOU'RE WISE ENOUGH.
WHO'D SHE MEAN BY "HIM"?
- ( grunting )
I'M GONNA GET YOU OUT OF THERE,
HAZUKI! I'M ALMOST THERE!
HAZUKI!
- THAT VOICE.
IT'S COMING FROM THE SKY.
- THE TIME HAS COME.
- WHO COULD IT BE?
IS IT THE MOON?
- ( grunting )
( screams )
HAZUKI? HAZUKI!
I'M SO GLAD YOU'RE OKAY.
YOU REALLY HAD ME WORRIED,
KID, YOU KNOW THAT?
- MY NAME IS LUNA.
- WHAT?
- THERE IS NO HAZUKI.
- MISTRESS LUNA HAS
AWAKENED NOW.
YOU'VE WASTED MY
TIME LONG ENOUGH.
- ( groaning )
- WHAT DO YOU MEAN "LUNA?"
STAND UP! WE'VE GOTTA GET
OUT OF THIS PLACE!
- I CAN'T GO. I'M STAYING HERE
WITH MY MOTHER FOREVER.
- LISTEN TO ME, HAZUKI.
YOU DON'T REALIZE
WHAT YOU'RE SAYING.
YOU'VE BEEN PUT INTO SOME
KIND OF A TRANCE.
COME ON! I'LL GET YOU
OUT OF HERE.
- Kinkel: A WEAKLING LIKE YOU
DOESN'T DESERVE HER.
- ELFRIEDE? IS THAT YOU?
WHAT WAS THAT VOICE?
ELFRIEDE, WHAT'S THE MATTER?
- SO THE OLD CONJUROR
WAS JUST A DECOY.
SO MUCH FOR THAT PLAN.
- BASTARD!
- WHAT A USELESS CREATURE.
- THIS IS YOUR CHANCE, HAZUKI,
JUST GET OUT OF HERE!
DON'T WORRY ABOUT ME, JUST GO!
- HERE'S A BETTER IDEA.
LET'S USE HIM TO TEST YOUR
AWAKENING, MISTRESS LUNA.
DESPAIR, THE AWARENESS OF
IMPENDING SUFFERING
WHEN YOU KNOW
YOU CANNOT PREVENT.
IT IS MY FAVORITE OF
HUMAN EMOTIONS.
- HAZUKI...
- WHY?
- AND TO CAUSE DESPAIR
IN THE ONE WHO TRIED
TO SAVE YOU,
NOTHING CAN BE MORE
BEAUTIFUL THAN THAT.
( maniacal laughter )
- THAT SMELL. BLOOD. HIS BLOOD.
I CAN REMEMBER THAT SMELL.
AND I WANT IT. I NEED IT.
- WHAT IS THIS POWER?
- HEY, WHAT HAPPENED?
WHERE AM I?
KOUHEI! WHAT'S GOING ON?
HOW'D WE GET HERE?
- HEY, BRAT.
- WHY ARE YOU LYING ON THE
FLOOR LIKE THAT, YOU DUMMY?
GET UP!
HEY, WHAT HAPPENED TO MY HAND?
- ABOUT TIME YOU
ACTED NORMAL AGAIN.
YOU CAN BE A REAL PAIN IN THE
ASS SOMETIMES, YOU KNOW THAT?
- BUT, WHAT IS THIS BLOOD FROM?
- AS POWERLESS AS I AM.
I THINK I WAS ACTUALLY
ABLE TO SAVE YOU,
IN A WEIRD SORT OF WAY.
- WHAT ARE YOU TALKING
ABOUT, KOUHEI?
- YOU WERE WORTH IT.
- KOUHEI? KOUHEI! WHAT'S WRONG?
- HE'S NOT A SLAVE AT ALL.
HE WAS SOMETHING ELSE. SO THIS
IS THE "HIM" ELFRIEDE SPOKE OF.
THE VAMPIRE'S LOVER.
- NO! BIG BROTHER, PLEASE!
- THEN IT ISN'T JUST A LEGEND.
A LUDO FAIRYTALE.
HE IS THE ONE MAN CAPABLE OF
WIPING OUT EVERYTHING
OUR KIND HAS BUILT.
OUR ENTIRE WAY OF LIFE.
HE'S OUR WORST NIGHTMARE.
AND HE MUST BE DESTROYED!
FORCES OF LIGHT THAT BIND
ALL CORNERS OF THE WORLD!
FUSE TOGETHER AND CAST
THE ENEMY TO THE HEART OF HELL.
PENETRATE THE ILLUSION.
BE CRUSHED BY THE LIGHT.
PURITY THAT BINDS ALL THE
CORNERS OF THE WORLD,
PIERCE THE HEART.
YOUR FATE BE SEALED!
WHAT'S THIS?
- ( coughing )
- MASTER!
- NO, KOUHEI...
PLEASE...
- STEP AWAY.
- NO! I'M NOT
LEAVING HIM! STOP!
- SEIJI, LET HER TELL US
WHAT HAPPENED.
- I'M NOT SURE. I WAS
DREAMING ABOUT MY MOTHER.
WE WERE SITTING BY A TREE,
WE WERE HAPPY. AND THEN...
AND THEN I HEARD KOUHEI'S
VOICE UP IN THE SKY.
I TRIED TO SEE HIM
BUT I COULDN'T.
AND WHEN I WOKE UP,
HE WAS ON THE FLOOR!
- HIS LEFT LUNG HAS BEEN
PUNCTURED. WE HAVE TO GO.
- ( gasps )
- AN UTTER FAILURE, SPURRED
BY TOO MANY UNKNOWNS.
BUT NOW THE TRUTH IS EXPOSED.
ORDER IN THE VAMPIRE
CLAN IS MAINTAINED BY
THE SACRED HIERARCHY, BUILT
ON THE POWER OF BLOOD TIES.
AND ORDER MUST BE RESTORED.
THIS SLAVE I CAN HANDLE.
SHE'LL LEARN THE PENALTY OF
TRYING TO ESCAPE
HER MASTER'S GRIP.
BUT AS FOR YOU, BOY...
- ( siren wailing )
- Kinkel: THE BREAKER OF BLOOD
TIES. THE VAMPIRE'S LOVER.
YOU'RE FAR TOO DANGEROUS
TO BE LEFT ALIVE.
- ( theme song playing )
- ( singing in French )
- BIG BROTHER,
I'M TIRED OF RIDDLES.
LET'S TRY SOMETHING ELSE THAT
CAN BE EVEN MORE FUN!
YA HAVE TO THINK AS HARD AS YOU
CAN, AND SEE IF YOU CAN
COME UP WITH SOMETHING
NO ONE'S EVER THOUGHT BEFORE!
YOU READY? FULL, FULL, FULL...
MOON! WELL?
DID YOU THINK OF SOMETHING
REALLY SMART AND ORIGINAL?
TELL YOU WHAT. WE BETTER MAKE
THAT YOUR HOMEWORK ASSIGNMENT.
SEEMS LIKE YOU'RE GONNA
HAVE A LOT OF TIME
TO THINK RIGHT NOW, ANYWAY.
NEXT, IT'S EPISODE 10,
"YOU'RE MY SLAVE AND
I WON'T FORGIVE YOU!"