- SO, IT WAS DECIDED WE WOULD
ALL TAKE A TRIP TO KYOTO.
HIROMI AND I NEEDED
TO COVER A STORY.
GRANDPA AND SEIJI HAD BUSINESS
WITH THE HEAD OF THE FAMILY.
AND HAZUKI, WELL,
SHE WAS ALONG FOR THE RIDE.
- OH! IT'S SO BEAUTIFUL!
ISN'T IT?
- THAT'S PERFECT.
THE BRAT ALREADY THINKS I'M HER
SLAVE, NOW I'M THEIRS TOO.
HERE'S YOUR BENTO, GUYS.
AND THESE ARE FOR THE GIRLS.
AW, COME ON! WOULD YOU TAKE
OFF THOSE STUPID NEKO MIMI?
WE'RE IN PUBLIC NOW!
YOU HAVING FUN, HAZUKI?
- ( laughs )
- YOUR FIRST TRIP
ON A TRAIN, HUH?
I'M GLAD I DIDN'T INSIST THAT
SHE STAY HOME, AFTER ALL.
- Hazumi: OOH!
THAT LOOKS YUMMY!
- AND THIS ONE'S THE SOY SAUCE,
SO MAKE SURE YOU DON'T
MIX 'EM UP, OKAY?
- BENTO IS THE COOLEST EVER!
( speaking Japanese )
- HOW MUCH LONGER CAN YOU LAST?
- KOUHEI MORIOKA,
THE TIME HAS COME.
- ( theme song playing )
- ( singing in Japanese )
- SO, THIS IS THE MIDO
FAMILY HOME, HUH?
SOMEHOW I EXPECTED MORE.
- YOU CAN'T TELL FROM OUT HERE,
BUT IT'S REALLY QUITE LARGE.
- WE'RE GOING IN THERE?
FOR REAL?
- UH, GRAMPS?
I THINK I'M GONNA STAY OUT HERE.
- OH, REALLY?
BUT THEY SERVE SUCH GOOD TEA.
- YOU SURE YOU WANNA
MISS ALL THE FUN, KOUHEI?
- YEAH. HAZUKI SEEMS
PRETTY NERVOUS.
- VERY WELL. DON'T WORRY.
WE'LL TAKE CARE OF EVERYTHING.
HAIJI WILL NEED TO COME WITH ME
FOR A LITTLE WHILE, ALL RIGHT?
- SURE, I GUESS SO.
BUT I STILL DON'T KNOW WHY.
- BROTHER SEIJI!
IT'S YOU, ISN'T IT?
- WELL, WELL, WELL.
HIKARU AND KAORU!
- I KNEW IT!
WHERE'VE YOU BEEN, SEIJI?
YOU'VE BEEN GONE FOREVER.
HAVE YOU MISSED ME?
- HELLO, HIKARU.
OF COURSE I HAVE.
- IT'S SO NICE TO SEE YOU AGAIN,
BIG BROTHER.
- YEAH, YOU TOO. YOU'RE
LOOKING REALLY GOOD, KAORU.
- OH, THANK YOU.
- WHO IS THIS MOUSE?
- OH, THAT'S RIGHT.
YOU HAVEN'T MET THESE
TWO YET, HAVE YOU, HAZUKI?
- MY NAME IS HIKARU MIDO.
I'M SEIJI'S SECOND COUSIN AND
THE WOMAN HE'S GONNA MARRY.
AND THIS IS MY LOVELY
TWIN SISTER, KAORU.
SHE'S ENGAGED TO KOUHEI.
- ( exclaims )
- WHAT DOES SHE MEAN "ENGAGED"?
YOU'RE ENGAGED?
- IS THAT TRUE, SENSEI?
- WELL, IT'S SORT OF
A CHILDHOOD THING...
- OUR FAMILIES PROMISED
US TO EACH OTHER
WHEN WE WERE
STILL LITTLE KIDS.
- IT'S A PROMISE THAT BINDS US
TOGETHER FOREVER.
- THAT'S OUT OF THE QUESTION!
KOUHEI IS MY SLAVE AND HE'S NOT
MARRYING ANYBODY, UNDERSTOOD?
- ( grunts )
I MEAN, HE'S VERY
IMPORTANT TO ME!
- BUT...
- WELL, HE'S IMPORTANT
TO US, TOO. AND WE HAVE DIBS.
- GUESS WE SHOULDN'T HAVE LEFT
THE HOUSE TODAY, HUH, HAZUKI?
- WHAT DID YOU JUST SAY?
- NOW YOU'VE DONE IT, MORON.
- ( crying )
- AW, COME ON NOW,
KAORU. DON'T CRY.
WHAT'D I SAY? I JUST TOLD HER WE
SHOULDN'T HAVE LEFT THE HOUSE.
- THAT'S RIGHT! HE JUST
SAID WE SHOULDN'T HAVE
LEFT THE HOUSE WHERE
WE LIVE TOGETHER.
- ( both gasp )
- YOU WANNA FIGHT?
BRING IT.
- THIS PLACE IS TOO PUBLIC FOR
A SORCERER'S BATTLE.
TAKE THE GIRL
AND GET OUT OF HERE.
- COME ON BRAT,
MAYBE WE CAN FIND SOME
ANGER MANAGEMENT CLASSES!
- HEY, KOUHEI, WAIT FOR ME!
- LET THEM GO.
- BUT KOUHEI'S IN DANGER! THAT
GIRL HE'S WITH IS A MONSTER.
- HE'S OKAY.
- ACTUALLY, WE NEED
YOU HERE, GIRLS.
YOU'RE JUST IN TIME TO TAKE
KOJIRO A MESSAGE FOR US.
- Hiromi: THE MIDO FAMILY HAS
ALWAYS BEEN FAMOUS
FOR THEIR PSYCHIC POWERS.
BEFORE RYUUHEI OPENED HIS
ANTIQUE SHOP,
HE WORKED AS A SPIRITUALIST.
AND SEIJI SENSEI STILL DOES.
KOUHEI GREW UP SURROUNDED
BY SPELLS AND CHARMS
HIS WHOLE LIFE SO HE
HARDLY NOTICES THEM.
AND I'VE HEARD SO MANY STORIES
EDITING THE MAGAZINE THAT
I SUPPOSE I TAKE THE PARANORMAL
FOR GRANTED SOMETIMES.
BUT SEEING THEIR
FAMILY IN ACTION
IS A WHOLE OTHER
STORY, ISN'T IT?
- SO THOSE TWO GIRLS ARE...
- AS PSYCHIC AS
THE REST OF THEM.
- NO WONDER I DIDN'T LIKE THEM.
ENGAGED? HMM.
- IT'S RIDICULOUS.
MY STUPID FAMILY AND ITS
STANDARDS. IT'S NOT RIGHT.
I MEAN IT'S NORMAL NOT
TO HAVE PSYCHIC POWERS
BUT WHEN YOU'RE IN A FAMILY FULL
OF PEOPLE WHO DO, IT'S LIKE...
- LIKE BEING THE DUMB ONE
IN A FAMILY OF GENIUSES.
- IT'S NOTHING AT ALL LIKE THAT!
- YOU POOR LITTLE
MISUNDERSTOOD IDIOT.
- YOU KNOW THAT'S
NOT WHAT I MEANT!
- THIS GIRL'S GOT
A POINT, KOUHEI.
YOU'RE A LUCKY JERK, AND IF
YOU DON'T STOP COMPLAINING
I'M GONNA START
THROWING THINGS AT YOU.
- I'M A LUCKY JERK?
HOW DO YOU FIGURE?
- YOU DON'T HAVE TO BE
PSYCHIC TO KNOW THAT ONE.
- SO KOUHEI TOOK HER
UNDER HIS WING.
AND THE CHILD'S BEEN LIVING
WITH US IN TOKYO EVER SINCE.
- A VAMPIRE.
THAT'S AN INTERESTING TALE.
- YOU MEAN AN
INTERESTING COINCIDENCE.
CONSIDERING WHAT MY
DAUGHTER SAID 14 YEARS AGO
ON THE NIGHT SHE DISAPPEARED.
- Chizuru: DAD, I KNOW IT
SOUNDS CRAZY,
BUT VAMPIRES EXIST,
I KNOW THEY DO.
- AND NOW THE PROOF OF HER
REMARKABLE CLAIM IS REVEALED.
- THE VAMPIRE CHILD IS NOT OUR
ONLY NEW HOUSE GUEST, KOJIRO.
THIS CAT'S NAME IS ACUDA.
IT WAS CHIZURU'S
SHIKIGAMI MESSENGER.
- IT WAS? HOW DO YOU KNOW?
- I DON'T KNOW YET HOW
THE CHILD'S MOTHER
COULD'VE GAINED POSSESSION
OF MY DAUGHTER'S SHIKIGAMI.
BUT I'M POSITIVE THIS IS ACUDA.
- IT SEEMS WEAK.
- YES. IT NEEDS ENERGY
FROM ITS MASTER
OR IT'LL DIE IN
THE NEXT FEW DAYS.
- I DON'T WANT TO LOSE
THIS CREATURE, KOJIRO.
IT'S MY ONLY LINK
TO MY DAUGHTER.
I CAME HERE FOR
THE FAMILY'S HELP.
PLEASE. WE CANNOT DO THIS ALONE.
- THE OCTAGONAL HALL
IS YOURS TO USE
FOR AS LONG AS YOU REQUIRE IT.
- THANK YOU.
- ( camera clicking )
- THERE HE IS.
"THE MYSTERIOUS
NOBLEMAN WHO HAUNTS
ONE OF KYOTO'S MOST
POPULAR RAMEN SHOPS."
NEXT MONTH'S FEATURE
HEADLINE JUST WROTE ITSELF.
- YOU DID IT, KOUHEI.
YOU SAVED THE HEADLINE.
YOU KNOW, TALENT IS VERY SEXY.
- I'M SO GLAD YOU THINK SO.
- ( crying ) I'M USING A
YOKOHAMA RAMEN RECIPE IN KYOTO.
THAT'S WHY THE NOBLEMAN
IS HAUNTING MY RESTAURANT!
- I STILL HAVE TO
INTERVIEW THIS GUY,
SO YOU TWO CAN HEAD
OUT NOW IF YOU WANT.
HERE YOU GO, HAZUKI,
YOUR FIRST COMMISSION.
THAT'S FOR ALL THE HELP
YOU GAVE US.
NOW WHY DON'T YOU LET KOUHEI
TAKE YOU SOUVENIR SHOPPING?
- WHAT? AND WHY SHOULD I?
- HEY, I WANTED TO TAKE A
WALKING TOUR OF KYOTO,
AND YOU'RE THE REASON WE GOT
HERE TOO LATE, COOKIE,
SO JUST SUCK IT UP AND
TAKE HER SHOPPING, OKAY?
- IT'S HAZUKI'S FAULT. SHE'S
THE ONE WHO HAS TO TRAVEL AT...
- TAKE ME SHOPPING!
- I'M SUCH A SUCKER.
- ( gasps )
- MAKE SURE YOU DON'T GET
TOO FAR FROM ME, OKAY?
- OKAY, DAD!
- HELLO, LITTLE LADY. WOULD YOU
LIKE TO TRY SOME YATSUHASHI?
CAN'T LEAVE KYOTO WITHOUT
TRYING OUR MOST FAMOUS DESSERT.
- IT'S ALL DRY AND FLAKYISH.
- THAT JUST MEANS IT'S
REALLY GOOD YATSUHASHI.
- OH! THEN I'LL TAKE
A WHOLE BOX.
- YOU HAVE EXCELLENT TASTE.
- BE CAREFUL. YOU DON'T
WANNA SPEND IT ALL HERE.
- DON'T WORRY.
GRANDFATHER GAVE ME A BUNCH
OF SPENDING MONEY, TOO.
- GREAT, THEY'RE TRYING
TO SPOIL YOU ROTTEN.
- I JUST LOVE THE SMELL
OF CINNAMON. DON'T YOU?
- ELFRIEDE!
- HEY! YOU FOLLOWED ME
ALL THE WAY TO KYOTO!
- IT'S NOT YOU I WAS FOLLOWING.
- THEN WHY ARE YOU HERE?
- FOR KOUHEI. I DID SAY
I'D MODEL FOR HIM, AFTER ALL.
AND WHAT BETTER PLACE THAN HERE?
WITH SUCH A
BREATHTAKING BACKDROP,
I JUST MIGHT REVEAL
MORE THAN I INTEND.
- BACK OFF, HAG!
GET YOUR OWN SLAVE!
- I SUPPOSE SINCE I AM HERE,
I SHOULD ASK YOU TO
RETURN TO THE CASTLE.
- JUST LEAVE US ALONE!
YOU SLAVE STEALER!
( grunting )
- OH DEAR, I SEEM TO HAVE
UPSET THE LITTLE DARLING.
I GUESS I BETTER GO BEFORE SHE
PUTS SOMEONE OUT OF BUSINESS.
CLEANUP ON AISLE 5!
- ( panting )
HE'S MINE!
- ALL RIGHT.
WHO'S PAYING FOR ALL THIS?
- UH, I AM SO SORRY, SIR!
I, UM... I'LL COVER IT.
DON'T WORRY.
- YOU BET YOU WILL, PAL.
I HOPE YOU HAVE CREDIT.
- Ryuuhei: WE'LL BORROW POWER
FROM THE MIDO FAMILY SHRINE
AND TRANSFER ACUDA'S
SPIRIT BOND TO A NEW MASTER.
THAT SHOULD BE ENOUGH
TO SAVE HIM.
- Seiji: THE ONLY PROBLEM IS
WHO SHOULD INHERIT IT?
YOU, AS CHIZURU'S FATHER,
OR KOUHEI, AS HER SON?
I SEE.
AND WHOSE HAIRS ARE THOSE?
- THEY BELONG TO THE GIRL.
- YOU'RE CERTAIN ABOUT THIS?
- KOUHEI AND I HAVE
A STRONG FAMILY,
PEOPLE WE CAN CONFIDE IN,
BUT THAT GIRL'S ALL ALONE.
SHE NEEDS A GOOD FRIEND.
- THEN LET'S BEGIN.
WE'VE A LONG NIGHT AHEAD.
- WHAT'S WRONG, HAZUKI?
- "3 A.M. AT AWAGI TEMPLE."
(gasps ) HAZUKI!
WHAT'RE YOU DOING HERE?
- I SHOULD BE ASKING YOU
THE SAME THING.
HOW COULD YOU MEET THAT NO-GOOD
SLAVE STEALING HUSSY
BEHIND MY BACK?
- HOW DID YOU KNOW THAT?
- I SAW THE NOTE!
- LOOK, THERE'S A GOOD REASON
FOR THIS, I PROMISE,
IT'S JUST THAT...
HEY! A GIANT BOX OF YATSUHASHI!
- REALLY? WHERE?
HEY! KOUHEI! THAT'S CHEATING!
GET BACK HERE! KOUHEI!
- I KNOW SEIJI SAID
TO LEAVE HER ALONE,
BUT WE CAN'T STAND
BY AND DO NOTHING
WHILE YOUR FIANCEE IS IN DANGER
AND DOESN'T EVEN REALIZE IT.
I WON'T LET THAT
DEMONIC GIRL HURT HIM.
LET'S GO, KAORU!
- ( whimpers )
- ( sighs ) OH, KAORU.
YOU'RE HOPELESS.
- MAY I ASK YOU
SOMETHING, UNCLE?
- OF COURSE.
- WHEN YOU TOLD KOUHEI ABOUT HIS
MOTHER, YOU SAID SHE WAS DEAD.
- YES.
HOW DO YOU TELL YOUR GRANDSON
THAT HIS MOTHER ABANDONED HIM
14 YEARS AGO, AND
DISAPPEARED FOREVER?
- Kouhei: I GUESS
SHE ALREADY LEFT.
( gasps )
YOU'RE HERE.
- I COULDN'T MAKE
YOU COME OUT HERE
IN THE MIDDLE OF THE NIGHT FOR
PICTURES, AND THEN NOT SHOW.
- HAVING YOU AS A MODEL
IS A NICE DREAM,
BUT THAT'S NOT
WHY I CAME HERE.
AND I KNOW THAT'S NOT WHY
YOU'RE HERE EITHER.
I CAME BECAUSE I WANNA
KNOW SOMETHING.
YOU KEEP ASKING HAZUKI TO GO
BACK TO THE CASTLE,
BUT YOU'RE NOT DOING
ANYTHING TO FORCE HER HAND.
YOU CALL HER "MISTRESS" LIKE
YOU'RE HER SERVANT OR SOMETHING,
BUT YOU'RE OBVIOUSLY
NOT DOING WHAT SHE WANTS.
I DON'T THINK YOU
MEAN HER ANY HARM,
BUT WHAT IS IT
YOU'RE AFTER, EXACTLY?
- ( sighs ) I SUPPOSE I'M
A LITTLE ENVIOUS.
- KOUHEI, COME ON.
I WANNA GO HOME.
THIS ISN'T FUNNY.
- Elfriede: THE WAY SHE LIVES,
SO CAREFREE.
YES, THAT'S IT. SO FREE.
- FREE?
- AND YOU'RE THE REASON
FOR THAT FEELING IN HER.
DID YOU KNOW THAT?
YOU'RE THE VAMPIRE'S LOVER.
IF ONLY I HAD SOMEONE
LIKE YOU IN MY LIFE, AS WELL.
- UM, ELFRIEDE, I CAN'T...
- SET ME FREE, KOUHEI.
- NO!
( screams )
- SET ME FREE FROM THAT MAN.
- THIS FEELING.
WHAT'S HAPPENING TO KOUHEI?
KOUHEI! KOUHEI, WHERE ARE YOU?
KOUHEI!
NO!
SO THAT'S WHY SHE WANTED YOU
TO MEET HER HERE WITHOUT ME.
WHY DIDN'T YOU JUST GO HOME
WHEN I TOLD YOU TO,
LIKE ANY OTHER SLAVE?
- WHEN ARE YOU GONNA GET IT
THROUGH YOUR HEAD, BRAT?
I'M NOT YOUR...
- KOUHEI? KOUHEI?
- GET AWAY FROM HIM! NOW!
- WHAT ARE YOU TWO DOING HERE?
- LET HIM GO. I WON'T LET
YOU GET AWAY WITH THIS!
FOUL TEMPTRESS.
YOU WON'T SEDUCE KOUHEI.
( grunting )
- NO, WAIT. IT WASN'T ME.
- RIGHT. LIAR!
- WAIT!
- I DON'T THINK YOU CAN TALK
YOUR WAY OUT OF THIS ONE,
MY DARLING MISTRESS.
- EVIL DEMON! LET'S SEE HOW
YOU BITE WITHOUT THOSE TEETH!
- I TOLD YOU IT WASN'T ME,
IT WAS ANOTHER VAMPIRE,
I SWEAR, I WAS JUST
TRYING TO HELP.
- OH, YEAH,
LIKE I'D BELIEVE YOU!
- GOODNESS, THAT GIRL
IS AWFULLY TALENTED.
THE MISTRESS IS
IN OVER HER HEAD.
- GET BACK HERE AND REPENT,
DEMON GIRL!
- YOU'RE CRAZY!
- OW, STOP!
MY HAND...
BUT HOW DID SHE DO THAT?
- MY BARRIER!
MY POWER WON'T LAST
UNLESS I HAVE MORE BLOOD.
THAT'S IT!
I HOPE YOU SAVED
SOME FOR ME, KOUHEI!
( gasps )
- AND LOOK, THE OTHER
ONE'S A CONJURER.
MY, WHAT AN INTERESTING FAMILY.
- WHAT IS THAT?
- NOTHING FOR IT, I GUESS. I'LL
HAVE TO PROTECT HER THIS TIME.
- WHAT'S THAT?
KAORU! NO! WHO'S DOING THIS?
- ELFRIEDE.
- IT'S BEGINNING.
WHAT HAPPENED?
- IT MUST'VE SENSED SOMETHING
OUT THERE. WE HAVE TO FOLLOW IT!
- IT'S DAYBREAK!
- IF IT'S LOOKING FOR
ITS NEW MASTER,
THE GIRL MIGHT BE
IN TROUBLE. FASTER!
- ( groaning )
HAZUKI, THE SUN, IT'S...
( gasps ) WHAT IS THAT?
- NO, IT'S...
IF THE SUN'S RAYS TOUCH US
WE'LL BOTH BE KILLED.
WE HAVE TO GET
OUT OF HERE, NOW!
RUN!
- REACH OUT YOUR HAND, MASTER.
NOW!
- OKAY.
- HEY, YOU GUYS, COME ON.
I FOUND HER. SHE'S OVER
HERE. HURRY IT UP!
- ( grunting )
- ( all screaming )
- SHE'S SAFE.
- WE MADE IT JUST IN TIME.
- TOO CLOSE FOR MY TASTE.
- WHY? THEY'RE NOT YOUR SLAVES,
WHY DO THEY PROTECT YOU?
- I DON'T LIKE IT IN HERE!
THESE COATS ARE STINKY!
- WELL DONE, BOYS!
- AND STOP SITTING ON ME!
- HIP-HIP HOORAY!
- SO I WANT YOU TO LEAVE HER
ALONE FROM NOW ON.
NO MORE FIGHTING. UNDERSTOOD?
- NO MORE FIGHTING,
GRANDPA. I PROMISE.
- THAT'S VERY ADULT
OF YOU. THANKS.
- OH, YOU'RE WELCOME.
IT'S NOTHING.
- AND NO MORE CRYING
EITHER, OKAY?
LIKE I TOLD YOU, THERE'S
NOTHING BETWEEN ME AND HAZUKI.
NOW YOU PROMISE YOU'LL COME
SEE US WHEN YOU'RE IN TOKYO.
THERE. THAT'S BETTER.
- Elfriede: YOU HAVE NO IDEA
HOW LUCKY YOU ARE.
LIVING AS YOU CHOOSE.
FREELY.
SELFISHLY.
YET LOVED BY THOSE AROUND YOU.
I ENVY YOU FOR THAT, MISTRESS.
WITH ALL THAT I AM.
- ( sighs ) I'M SO EXHAUSTED.
- YOU WANT SOME MORE NOW, HAIJI?
SHE'S SO CUTE.
I'M GONNA KEEP HER FOREVER.
- YOU SEEM HAPPY TOGETHER.
I'M GLAD.
- YES. JUST A PITY THE
TRANSFER OF MASTERS
ERASED THE SPIRIT'S
MEMORY OF THE PAST.
- COULDN'T BE HELPED.
- Haiji: EXCEPT HIM!
I REMEMBER YOU FROM BEFORE.
YOU'RE NICE.
SO I'LL PROTECT YOU
AND MY MASTER NOW.
AND KEEP YOU COMPANY
SINCE YOUR MOM IS GONE.
OKEY-DOKEY?
- I'LL COUNT ON IT.
- HEY, YOU STAY AWAY. SHE'S MY
SHIKIGAMI AND WE'RE INSEPARABLE.
TRY A BEAN, HAIJI. DON'T
FORGET, LITTLE BITES, OKAY?
- Haiji: LITTLE BITES.
- (theme song playing )
- ( singing in Japanese )
- Hazuki: OKAY, BIG BROTHER.
IT'S RIDDLE TIME AGAIN.
( sternly ) IT'S RIDDLE TIME!
SIT DOWN!
NOW, WHAT GETS WETTER
AND WETTER THE MORE IT DRIES?
DON'T ROLL YOUR EYES.
IT'S A GOOD ONE.
READY? FULL, FULL, FULL MOON!
THIS IS AN EASY ONE, KOUHEI!
A TOWEL!
NEXT TIME ON MOON PHASE,
EPISODE 7,
"WELL, I WANTED IT..."
GOODNIGHT, BIG BROTHER!