- Kouhei: GRANDPA!
GRANDPA!
- ( coughing )
YOU'VE GOT TO STOP KOUHEI!
IT'S KINKEL!
HE'S... HE'S...
A DAY WALKER!
- ( theme song playing )
- ( singing in Japanese )
- ( gasping )
- ( groaning )
- KOUHEI!
- MISTRESS, DON'T!
- LET ME GO! I CAN'T JUST
WATCH HIM KILL KOUHEI.
- GETTING YOURSELF KILLED
BY THE SUN WON'T HELP ANYTHING.
- ( Kouhei groaning )
- YOU'VE SEEN SOME OF
WHAT THE COUNT CAN DO.
TAKING ON OTHER FORMS.
THAT'S HIS GREATEST POWER.
HE CAN BEND THE LIGHT
SURROUNDING HIM
TO CREATE AN IMAGE.
ANY APPEARANCE HE CHOOSES.
OR JUST CURVE THE RAYS
AROUND HIMSELF.
DISAPPEAR ENTIRELY.
MAKE IT SO THE SUNLIGHT
NEVER TOUCHES HIS BODY AT ALL.
- ( gasping )
- THAT'S HOW HE'S SURVIVED
FOR 900 YEARS,
THROUGH PLAGUES,
HUNTS, CRUSADES.
HE'S MASTERED THE MOST VALUABLE
POWER ANY VAMPIRE CAN POSSESS.
HE'S A DAY WALKER.
- ( gasping )
SO THIS WAS ALL
JUST ANOTHER TRAP?
TO GET KOUHEI
OUT THERE ON HIS OWN?
- BY USING SOMEONE KOUHEI LOVES.
THAT'S HOW THE COUNT WORKS.
- BUT WHY?
WHY DOES HE PLAY THESE GAMES
TO MAKE PEOPLE HURT?
- ( thinking ) BECAUSE THAT'S
WHAT YOU LOVE.
THE PAIN YOU CAN CAUSE
IN THESE HUMANS YOU DESPISE.
BY TOYING WITH EMOTIONS
YOU'VE NEVER UNDERSTOOD.
ISN'T THAT RIGHT? FATHER.
- TAIRAIFU!
WHERE'D HE GO?
( groaning )
- YOU CHILDREN ARE
BEGINNING TO BORE ME.
TIME TO SAY GOODBYE,
VAMPIRE'S LOVER.
- KINKEL! YOU BASTARD.
- OH. SO YOU CAN STILL TALK.
YOU HURT... SEIJI.
- AND THAT'S WHY YOU'RE UPSET?
( laughs )
YOU HUMANS. ALWAYS SO NOBLE
WHEN YOU'RE ABOUT TO DIE.
- ( screaming )
- AND MAKE NO MISTAKE.
YOU WILL DIE.
NO AMOUNT OF NOBILITY
WILL SAVE YOU.
- WHY?
- WHY? BECAUSE, YOU SEE, BOY,
I CANNOT ALLOW AN ABOMINATION
LIKE YOU TO CONTINUE LIVING.
A WOULD-BE SLAVE WITH THE
POWER OF A VAMPIRE'S LOVER.
SUCH AN ABSURDITY
IS NOT TO BE BORN!
- ( screaming )
- Hazuki: LEAVE HIM ALONE!
LEAVE KOUHEI ALONE
AND I'LL GO WITH YOU.
- IS THAT SO?
- THAT'S WHAT YOU WANT.
FOR ME TO COME BACK
TO THE CASTLE.
WELL, I WILL, BUT ONLY
IF YOU LET HIM GO.
- ARE YOU TRYING TO
BARGAIN WITH ME?
- DO YOU WANT ME TO
COME BACK WITH YOU OR NOT?
IF YOU KILL HIM
I'LL NEVER GO WITH YOU. NEVER!
- I'M AFRAID THIS VIRUS
IS TOO MUCH OF A THREAT
TO LEAVE LYING AROUND.
HE WILL BRING CHAOS TO
THE ENTIRE VAMPIRE ORDER.
JUST LOOK WHAT HE DID TO THAT
TRAITOROUS WOMAN NEXT TO YOU.
- YOU FORGET, FATHER, WHO
I LEARNED MY TREACHERY FROM.
- Hazuki: I SEE.
WELL THEN, THAT MEANS
I HAVE NO CHOICE.
MISTRESS, BE CAREFUL!
- STAY BACK! I HAVE ONE THING TO
BARGAIN WITH THAT HE CAN'T RISK.
ISN'T THAT RIGHT, COUNT?
I HAVE MY LIFE.
WELL?
- Kinkel: ( thinking ) I BELIEVE
SHE'S SERIOUS.
WHAT IS THIS BOY TO HER?
VAMPIRE'S LOVER OR NOT, TO HER
HE SHOULD JUST BE A SLAVE.
WHAT WOULD DRIVE HER TO
SACRIFICE HER OWN LIFE
FOR A MORTAL? CURIOUS.
- WAIT. HE'S...
( gasping )
SUMMON!
- ELFRIEDE!
- FOOL.
- IF I'M A FOOL FOR WANTING
TO FREE MYSELF FROM YOU,
THEN I CHOOSE TO
REVEL IN MY FOOLISHNESS.
- ( laughs )
YOU REALLY THOUGHT
YOU COULD HURT ME?
- Ryuuhei: KOUHEI, RUN!
GOGYOU HAKKI!
- ( explosion booms )
- ( groaning )
GRANDPA?
- DON'T WORRY ABOUT ME.
- GRANDPA! OH MY GOSH!
THANK GOODNESS.
ARE YOU ALL RIGHT?
- ( Kinkel laughing )
WELL, CONGRATULATIONS.
YOU CAUGHT ME BY SURPRISE.
I THINK THAT DESERVES AN AWARD.
TELL YOU WHAT.
HAND OVER MISTRESS LUNA
AND THE VAMPIRE'S LOVER.
AND THE REST OF YOU
CAN ESCAPE WITH YOUR LIVES.
- ( sarcastically ) HOW KIND.
- CALL IT A GIFT OF GOODWILL.
I'LL EVEN GIVE YOU
TIME TO THINK IT OVER.
TWO HOURS.
( chuckling )
- I DON'T UNDERSTAND.
WHY NOT FINISH THIS
BEFORE WE HAVE TIME TO PLAN?
- Elfriede: BECAUSE IT'S
A GAME TO HIM.
HE'S TOYING WITH US.
ENJOYING THE POWER.
HE WANTS US TO SUFFER
BEFORE WE DIE.
- Seiji: I'M SORRY I...
I WASN'T MUCH USE OUT THERE.
- ( meows )
- DON'T BEAT YOURSELF UP.
I DON'T THINK THERE'S
ANYONE ON EARTH
WHO COULD'VE DEFEATED
HIM WITHOUT ANY HELP.
RIGHT, HAZUKI?
- HMM.
WHAT IS THIS?
- Seiji: IT'S A TALISMAN
THAT WARDS AGAINST IMPOSTERS.
I PUT UP A SPIRITUAL BARRIER
SO THE COUNT WON'T BE
ABLE TO SNEAK IN HERE.
EVEN IF HE TRIES TO
APPEAR IN DISGUISE
OR MAKE HIMSELF INVISIBLE,
IN HERE, HE'LL APPEAR
IN HIS TRUE FORM.
- SO, WE'RE SAFE FOR A WHILE,
AT LEAST. THAT'S GOOD.
- SURE. WE'RE SAFE FOR A WHILE.
BUT WE CAN'T STAY LOCKED UP
IN THIS ROOM FOREVER, RIGHT?
- RIGHT, BUT HOW DO WE LEAVE
WHEN WE KNOW HE'S
WAITING RIGHT OUTSIDE?
WE HAVE NO WAY OF KNOWING
WHEN OR IF HE SLEEPS,
NOW THAT WE KNOW
HE'S A DAY WALKER.
- SO WE DO STAY HERE FOREVER.
- WELL, YOU CAN IF YOU WANT.
BUT I'VE BEEN AWAY
FROM THE ANTIQUE STORE
JUST ABOUT LONG ENOUGH.
I'M STARTING TO MISS
THE SMELL OF THE PLACE,
SO I THINK I'LL BE HEADING
HOME NOW IF YOU DON'T MIND.
WELL, HOW 'BOUT IT, KIDS? READY?
- SO YOU THINK WE SHOULD FIGHT.
- IT'S NOT A MATTER OF "IF."
THE ONLY REAL QUESTION IS "HOW."
- THERE'S JUST ONE WAY.
IF YOU REALLY WANT TO DEFEAT HIM
YOU'LL HAVE TO HURT HIM
WHILE HE'S IN THE SUNLIGHT.
WITH PAIN DISTRACTING HIM,
HE WON'T BE ABLE TO
DIVERT ALL THE RAYS.
THEN IF YOU'RE LUCKY,
AND IF THE WOUND YOU GIVE HIM
IS DEEP AND PAINFUL ENOUGH,
THE SUN WILL DO
THE REST OF THE WORK.
IF HE CAN'T FIND
SHELTER QUICKLY,
HE'LL BURN TO DEATH
WITHIN MINUTES.
- BUT HOW? HOW DO WE HURT
HIM? I MEAN, WE HAVEN'T YET.
- WELL, NOW,
I MAY KNOW A FEW TRICKS.
- ( clock ticking )
- ( clock chiming )
- MIGHT WORK.
- IT'S GOOD. I'D SAY IT'S THE
ONLY WAY WE STAND A CHANCE.
- KOUHEI?
I DON'T WANT A NEW SLAVE,
SO BE CAREFUL, OKAY?
PROMISE ME YOU WILL.
- YEAH.
- I DON'T WANT A NEW SLAVE,
SO BE CAREFUL, OKAY?
PROMISE ME YOU WILL.
- ( laughs ) I SEE,
MISTRESS LUNA.
THAT'S WHY YOU'RE
SO DETERMINED TO SAVE HIM.
YOU'VE FALLEN VICTIM
TO THEIR WEAKNESS.
I'M GLAD I GAVE THEM THIS TIME.
( laughs )
THIS IS GOING TO BE EVEN
MORE FUN THAN I ANTICIPATED.
- Ryuuhei: I WOULD SAY
WE CAN'T HAVE TOO MANY.
BETTER SAFE THAN SORRY.
- Seiji: GREAT.
HOW AM I SUPPOSED TO FIGHT
WITH WRITER'S CRAMP?
- NEXT TIME DON'T LET YOURSELF
GET OUT OF PRACTICE.
- Hazuki: IT'S ABOUT TEN MINUTES
FROM HERE TO THE LAKE.
IT MIGHT ONLY TAKE FIVE
IF YOU RUN.
- THERE'S MORE THAN ENOUGH
WATER THERE, THAT'S FOR SURE.
THIS JUST MIGHT WORK.
IT HAS TO WORK.
OKAY, HERE GOES NOTHIN'!
( gasps )
I'LL BE FINE. BACK BEFORE
YOU KNOW IT, KID.
- DON'T WORRY, MISTRESS.
KOUHEI WILL BE ALL RIGHT.
BOTH OF US ARE
WATCHING OVER HIM NOW.
- THANK YOU, ELFRIEDE.
- ( shouting ) HEY! KINKEL!
YOU PAYIN' ATTENTION?
'CAUSE HERE'S THE DEAL!
YOU CAN KILL ME IF YOU WANT,
BUT YOU LEAVE HAZUKI OUT OF IT.
SHE'S JUST A KID, AND SHE'S
NEVER DONE ANYTHING TO ANYONE.
ARE YOU HEARIN' ME?
YOU STAY AWAY FROM HER!
JUST LET HER WALK!
I'M THE ONLY ONE WHO'S
A THREAT TO YOUR KIND.
SO, WE HAVE A DEAL OR NOT?
( thinking ) DAMN IT.
MAYBE HE'S ON TO US.
COME ON.
- TELL ME. DID YOU
HONESTLY THINK
THAT I WOULD ACCEPT THIS DEAL?
FAREWELL.
- Ryuuhei: GOGYOU SOSHOU!
DOSHOUGON!
- THAT LIGHT. WHAT IS IT?
- ( thinking ) LET'S SEE HOW YOU
HANDLE THIS ONE, COUNT.
GOLD SHARDS,
PULLED FROM THE EARTH.
ENOUGH TO REFRACT
THE LIGHT AROUND YOU
AND MAKE IT DIFFICULT
TO MAINTAIN YOUR FACADE.
NOW, SHOW US YOUR TRUE SELF!
- ( Kinkel laughing )
- IT WAS JUST AN ILLUSION.
- THE REAL ONE MUST BE NEARBY.
GOGYOU SOSHOU. DOSHOUGON!
( gasping )
- ELFRIEDE, NOW!
- SUMMON!
- Kinkel: ELFRIEDE.
YOU REALLY THINK YOU CAN KILL
ME WITH A SIMPLE INCARNATION?
- ( thinking ) ALL I NEED TO DO
IS KEEP HIM STILL FOR A WHILE.
- Seiji: THERE!
GOGYOU SOSHOU.
SUISHOMOKU!
- ( laughs )
HOLD ME HERE
AS LONG AS YOU WANT.
WHAT GOOD WILL IT DO
YOU WHEN YOU HAVE NO WEAPON?
- OH, BUT WE DO, KINKEL.
- WHAT?
- SURELY YOU KNOW
THE ELEMENTS ARE CLOSELY TIED.
WE ALREADY MADE GOLD.
FROM EARTH!
NOW LET'S SEE IF WE CAN MAKE
WOOD FROM WATER!
- NO!
- FINISH HIM.
AND I'LL BE FREE.
- COME ON.
- ( both coughing )
- KOUHEI? GRANDPA!
- ( Ryuuhei coughing )
HERE!
- Kouhei: WE DID IT, HAZUKI!
KINKEL IS DEAD!
- THEN IT'S OVER?
- COME ON. I WANNA
WATCH YOU BURN, YOU BASTARD.
THERE'S NO ESCAPING
DEATH THIS TIME.
THE SUN CAN SEE YOU
FOR WHAT YOU ARE.
- ( Ryuuhei screaming )
- GRANDPA, NO!
- KOUHEI! WHAT HAPPENED?
IS HE ALL RIGHT?
- GOGYOU SOSHOU! DOSHOUGON!
- A FAKE!
- ( groaning )
- ELFRIEDE, NO!
- KOUHEI!
ARE YOU HURT?
- LOOK OUT!
- SEIJI!
- PLEASE, NO.
- Kinkel: THIS ISN'T OVER.
- I GUESS HE GOT HURT, TOO.
- NO, HE'S GETTING AWAY.
- HE WAS TRYING TO
GET OUT OF THE SUNLIGHT.
HE'S STILL ALIVE,
AND I'M GOING AFTER HIM.
- WAIT! NO!
- NO, DON'T GO. IT'S A TRAP!
- Kouhei: HAZUKI!
- ( gasping )
- HAZUKI, WHAT ARE YOU THINKING,
COMING UP HERE ON YOUR OWN?
- I WANT YOU TO
GET OUT OF HERE, KOUHEI.
- AH, GOOD, YOU'VE BOTH ARRIVED.
- Kouhei: SHOW YOURSELF!
- PUT HIM DOWN!
- ( Kinkel laughs )
WELCOME TO THE CLOSING ACT,
MY FRIENDS.
- KINKEL!
- BUT THERE'S SO MUCH BLOOD.
HOW CAN YOU BE...
- ( laughs )
DON'T BELIEVE EVERYTHING
YOU SEE, DEAR.
THE BLOOD'S REAL,
BUT IT'S CERTAINLY NOT MINE.
I KNEW YOU'D FOLLOW ME
IF YOU BELIEVED I WAS HURT,
DREAMING YOU COULD
FINISH ME OFF.
I WANTED TO MAKE SURE THIS FINAL
SCENE HAD A SMALLER AUDIENCE.
SO YOU COULD GIVE
YOUR PAIN TO ME AND ME ALONE.
- MY PAIN?
- YES. LET ME
DEMONSTRATE, SHALL I?
- ( gasping )
- I'M TOLD THE MOST PAINFUL
EXPERIENCE ON EARTH
IS LOSING THE ONE YOU LOVE.
- LEAVE HIM ALONE!
LET GO!
- IT'S TOO LATE.
YOU ALREADY SEALED
HIS FATE A LONG TIME AGO.
FROM THE TIME YOU
ACCEPTED THE HELP
OF THIS HUMAN
AND HIS FRIENDS,
YOU WERE HEADED TOWARD
THIS VERY MOMENT.
YOU CHOSE HIS DEATH
WHEN YOU CHOSE HIM.
- NO.
- ( sinister laugh )
- NO, PLEASE!
- AH, AH, AH.
WATCH YOUR STEP, MISTRESS.
NOW PAY ATTENTION
TO THE GRAND FINALE.
I'D HATE FOR YOU
TO MISS THIS PART,
WHEN YOU WORKED
SO HARD TO CAUSE IT.
- HAZU... KI!
( screaming )
- KOUHEI.
- THERE IS SUCH BEAUTY IN PAIN.
IN THE ANGUISH OF DEATH
AND THE IMPOTENCE OF GUILT.
WHY AM I THE ONLY ONE
WHO SEES IT?
( chuckling )
- YOU'RE RIGHT.
IT IS MY FAULT HE'S DYING.
I CAUSED IT ALL.
NO.
KOUHEI WON'T DIE
BECAUSE OF ME.
AND HE WON'T DIE
BECAUSE OF YOU EITHER!
- ( loud crashing )
- NO!
( yells )
YOU STUPID CHILD.
- Elfriede: YOU TALKED
ABOUT THE LOOK IN MY EYES
WHEN YOU'D HURT ME.
NEVER KNOWING IF I WAS
BEGGING FOR MERCY OR FOR MORE.
BUT THIS IS WHAT
I WAS BEGGING FOR.
TO SEE THAT FEAR IN YOU.
- ELFRIEDE!
- SUMMON!
- YOU DARE ATTACK YOUR MASTER?
YOU TRAITOR!
( screaming )
- I ALREADY TOLD YOU.
I'VE CHOSEN TO
REVEL IN MY FOOLISHNESS, FATHER.
- ( screaming )
YOU'RE NOTHING!
AND I AM A BLUE BLOOD!
DAMN YOU!
I'VE LIVED FOR 900 YEARS.
YOU'LL NEVER KILL ME!
NEVER! NEVER.
NEVER...
- OH, MAN!
- AN AGE OF TORMENT HAS ENDED.
AFTER 900 YEARS, COUNT HEINRICH
VON KINKEL IS FINALLY DEAD.
YOU TWO OKAY?
- YEAH.
- WE SHOULD GO DOWNSTAIRS,
CHECK IN WITH THE OTHERS,
TELL THEM IT'S OVER.
- KOUHEI?
I'M GLAD YOU DIDN'T DIE.
BUT YOU THINK NEXT
TIME YOU COULD DO IT
WITHOUT WORRYING
ME SO MUCH?
- RIGHT.
- ( thinking ) LET THEM REST.
THEY DESERVE IT.
- ( wind whooshing )
- GOODBYE...
FATHER.
- ( theme song playing )
- ( singing in Japanese )
- Kinkel: ALL RIGHT, MISTRESS.
A PARTING RIDDLE FOR YOU.
GIVE ME AIR AND I LIVE, GIVE
ME WATER AND I DIE. WHAT AM I?
I'M SURE YOU'LL HAVE
NO PROBLEM WITH THIS ONE.
FULL, FULL, FULL MOON.
NEXT TIME ON MOON PHASE.
EPISODE 14.
"BIG BROTHER,
WILL YOU WALK WITH ME?"
HAVE YOU GUESSED THE ANSWER YET?
FIRE.
GOODBYE, MISTRESS...
FOR NOW.