- EIGHT MONTHS AND NOTHING
IS CHANGED AT ALL.
YOU'D THINK THE CITY
COULD CLEAN THE LOT
SO IT WOULDN'T BE AN EYESORE.
- HEY, WHAT DO YOU THINK
YOU'RE DOING?
STOP IT, CHIEF.
YOU'RE KNEELING DOWN
LIKE IT'S A GRAVE!
THEY'RE NOT DEAD,
YOU UNDERSTAND ME?
QUIT ACTING LIKE THEY ARE.
- HIROMI, COME ON.
- THEY'RE ALIVE, ALL OF THEM.
I JUST HAVEN'T FOUND THEM YET,
THAT'S ALL.
- IF THEY'RE ALIVE
THEN WHY HAVEN'T THEY
GOTTEN IN TOUCH WITH YOU,
EVEN ONCE IN ALL THIS TIME?
YOU AREN'T EXACTLY A STRANGER.
LET THEM GO.
- LET THEM GO, CHIEF?
THEY'RE ALIVE!
THERE MUST BE A GOOD REASON
WHY THEY CAN'T GET
IN CONTACT WITH ME.
MAYBE THEY'RE IN TROUBLE.
- IN TROUBLE WITH WHOM?
RYUUHEI, SEIJI, ELFRIEDE,
KOUHEI, AND HAZUKI.
HARDLY A LIST OF USUAL SUSPECTS
RUNNING FROM THE LAW.
WHAT REASON WOULD THEY
HAVE TO SUDDENLY DISAPPEAR?
LIKE WE DON'T HAVE
ENOUGH MYSTERIES
TO DEAL WITH IN
OUR OWN MAGAZINE.
- HIROMI, CHIEF,
FORGIVE US.
WE JUST NEED A LITTLE MORE TIME.
- ( theme song playing )
- ( singing in Japanese )
- Hazuki: "DAY ON THE MOUNTAIN,
MONKEY IN THE SPA,
"THE CAT'S WHISKERS...
AND WHO ARE YOU?"
I GO UP THE MOUNTAIN
ONCE A MONTH.
FOR ONE DAY,
I'M ALLOWED TO SEE KOUHEI.
AND I'M ALLOWED
TO KISS HIM, TOO.
- ( grunting )
- HAS YOUR THIRST
BEEN QUENCHED, HAZUKI?
- YES, FOR NOW, AT LEAST.
- I UNDERSTAND KOUHEI SAVED
YOU FROM SOME TROUBLE.
-HE USED A SPELL, MASTER YAYOI!
I DIDN'T KNOW HE COULD DO THAT!
- CONSIDERING WHERE HE STARTED,
THAT'S CERTAINLY PROGRESS.
BUT OUR BOY'S STILL
WEAKER THAN A BABY BIRD.
- CAN'T WE AT LEAST SAY
I'M LIKE A LION CUB?
- YOU'RE NO CAT, SLAVE BOY.
- MIND YOUR OWN
BUSINESS, MIDGET.
I'M DOIN' THE BEST
I CAN OUT HERE, OKAY.
- ( laughs )
I HAVE NO DOUBT THAT YOU BELIEVE
THAT TO BE TRUE, KOUHEI.
THAT'S JUST PROOF YOU HAVE
A LONG WAY TO GO, MY FRIEND.
- ( all laughing )
- HEY, CATGIRL.
WHAT'RE YOU LAUGHING AT?
- I ONLY LAUGH AT YOU
'CAUSE I LOVE YOU, SLAVE BOY!
- YAYOI IS THE HEAD OF THE
MAIN BRANCH OF THE MIDO FAMILY.
I DON'T UNDERSTAND HOW
ALL THE BRANCHES CONNECT,
BUT NO ONE ARGUES
THAT IN THE MIDO CLAN,
YAYOI'S NUMBER ONE, AT LEAST
THAT'S WHAT HIKARU TOLD ME.
- Kouhei: GO AWAY?
WHY DO I HAVE TO DO THAT?
- KOUHEI...
- I'M SORRY BUT I DON'T SEE HOW
BEING SEPARATED FROM HAZUKI
IS GOING TO HELP ME
WITH MY TRAINING!
I DIDN'T ABANDON GRANDPA
JUST SO I COULD COME HERE
AND ABANDON HER, TOO!
- NOW JUST HOLD ON.
DO YOU HONESTLY THINK
YOU COULD PROTECT HER
IF SHE WAS ATTACKED RIGHT NOW?
- ( sighs )
- I THOUGHT THE POINT
OF YOUR TRAINING
WAS THAT YOU KNEW YOU COULDN'T.
- KOUHEI...
- THERE'S NO NEED TO WORRY.
WHILE YOU'RE WORKING
TO GET STRONGER,
I WILL PROTECT HAZUKI.
REAL TRAINING REQUIRES SOLITUDE.
YOU MUST BE SELF-RELIANT
THAT IS A RULE THAT
CANNOT BE COMPROMISED.
EITHER OBEY IT OR LEAVE
THE MOUNTAIN NOW.
- DO WHAT HE SAYS, BIG BROTHER.
I'LL BE OKAY.
- BUT I SWORE.
- PLEASE, KOUHEI. TRAIN HARD
AND GET STRONGER, ALL RIGHT?
I NEED A SLAVE I CAN DEPEND ON.
THAT'S WHAT YOU SAID
ON OUR TRIP, ISN'T IT?
SO, PINKIE SWEAR.
PROMISE YOU'LL DO YOUR BEST
TO GET STRONGER QUICKLY.
IT'S GONNA BE REALLY
BORING AROUND HERE
WITHOUT YOU TO SCREAM AT.
- HAZUKI.
- COME ON. PINKY SWEAR.
- YEAH, OKAY.
- PINKIE SWEAR, IF YOU LIE,
CROSS YOUR HEART, HOPE TO DIE,
A THOUSAND NEEDLES IN YOUR EYE!
YOU REALLY ARE DOING YOUR BEST,
RIGHT, KOUHEI?
HEY, WHAT ARE YOU DOING?
- ( groaning )
- SHE'S SUCKING HIS BLOOD!
- CUT IT OUT, YOU FRUITCAKE!
- NO NEED FOR NAME-CALLING.
- TASTES LIKE IRON.
- WELL, WHAT WERE YOU EXPECTING?
MAPLE SYRUP?
- UH, THAT WAS UNEXPECTED.
- I'LL SAY. WHAT'S YOUR PROBLEM?
WHY DIDN'T YOU STOP HER?
- IT HAPPENED SO FAST,
I WAS CAUGHT OFF GUARD.
- MASTER YAYOI,
HE NEEDS LOTS MORE TRAINING.
- THAT'S WHAT I SAID.
- MORE TRAINING FOR SLAVE BOY.
- REALLY KAORU,
WHAT WAS THAT ABOUT?
- BECAUSE IT JUST ISN'T FAIR.
HAZUKI GETS TO, YOU KNOW...
- OH NO.
- THIS ISN'T GOOD.
- OH! SHE'S JUST LIKE YOU,
MASTER, LOOK.
- ( mewing )
- UM, KAORU?
- ( purring )
- SHE'S SO CUTE.
TELL HER SHE'S CUTE, KOUHEI.
OH PLEASE, JUST SAY IT.
- UH. OKAY. KAORU. YOU'RE...
- HAVE TO BUTT IN,
DON'T YA, FANGS?
- THAT'S RIGHT!
- YOU'RE SO CUTE WITH YOUR
CAT EARS. OH, YES YOU ARE.
- I HAVE A TAIL TOO.
LOOK AT MY CUTE LITTLE TAIL.
- PERFECT. LOOK, SEE?
IT'S A CATTAIL.
HEY, BONEHEAD!
WHY AREN'T YOU LOOKING?
TELL HER HOW CUTE
SHE IS, KOUHEI!
- OKAY, UH, YOU'RE...
- LET HIM SAY IT.
- NOT A CHANCE.
- DEMON!
- THAT ALL YA GOT?
- WOULD YOU TWO STOP?
- ALL RIGHT, FIGHTERS!
TAKE YOUR PLACES, PLEASE! READY?
- MY GOODNESS, KOUHEI.
MUST BE NICE TO BE SO POPULAR.
- NO, IT'S NOT! ARE YOU CRAZY?
- MASTER YAYOI, IS THERE
SOMETHING WRONG? WHAT IS IT?
- HIKARU. KAORU.
COME OUTSIDE WITH ME.
- HUH?
- OKAY.
- YES, HAIJI, YOU TOO.
- WAY AHEAD OF YA!
- WHAT ABOUT US?
- YEAH, SENSEI,
DON'T JUST LEAVE US HERE.
- QUIET!
CAN'T YOU SEE
I'M TRYING TO HELP YOU?
THAT'S BETTER.
- Hikaru: MASTER YAYOI,
WHAT IS IT?
- Yayoi: SOMEONE
HAS BROKEN THROUGH
THE FIRST BARRIERS
AROUND  THE MOUNTAIN.
- Haiji: UH-OH.
- I NEED TO CHECK IT OUT.
I WANT YOU GIRLS TO MAKE SURE
HAZUKI NEVER GETS
OUT OF YOUR SIGHT.
- Girls: YES, SIR!
- HAIJI, COME WITH ME.
- CAN DO!
- AND NOW IT BEGINS.
- ( Kouhei clears throat )
SO, UH, ANYWAY,
HERE WE ARE.
- HERE YOU GO!
YOUR RICE FOR THE NEXT MONTH.
AND THEN, I KNOW YOU'RE SUPPOSED
TO BE SELF-SUFFICIENT AND ALL,
BUT WITH NOTHING BUT RICE
AND MOUNTAIN FERNS TO EAT
YOU AREN'T GETTING
A VERY BALANCED DIET,
SO I THOUGHT I'D
HELP YOU OUT A BIT.
TA-DA!
- GEEZ, WHAT'D YOU DO,
ROB A DRUGSTORE?
I JUST ASKED GRANDMOTHER
KOHARU TO ORDER THEM FOR ME.
I SAID I WANTED THEM
ALL FOR MYSELF.
CONSIDERING THAT I'M THE MASTER
AND YOU'RE THE SLAVE,
I SPEND AN AWFUL LOT OF TIME
LOOKING AFTER YOU.
DON'T WORRY, YOU CAN PAY
ME FOR EVERYTHING LATER,
IT'S NO PROBLEM.
I KEPT THE RECEIPT.
- THANKS, HAZUKI,
THIS MEANS A LOT TO ME.
- WELL, I CAN'T HAVE MY
FOOD SOURCE MALNOURISHED.
- YOU'RE SUCH A LITTLE BRAT.
- ( giggles )
- SO, WANNA GO FOR A WALK?
- SURE.
- IT'S COLD OUT, THOUGH.
DID YOU BRING A JACKET?
- I'M FINE.
- ( wind blowing )
- VAMPIRES, THIS MOUNTAIN IS
UNDER THE CARE OF
THE MIDO FAMILY.
YOU WILL NOT HAVE YOUR WAY.
- Jeda: WE'RE GOING IN CIRCLES.
NO MATTER HOW FAR WE WALK,
WE END UP IN THE SAME PLACE.
WHOEVER IS PROTECTING
MISTRESS LUNA
HAS PUT SOME KIND
OF SPELL ON US.
- SOME KIND OF EASTERN MAGIC?
- SO IT WOULD SEEM,
AND VERY POWERFUL, TOO.
- FEELS...SO...GOOD...
OH, COZY.
- WELL, GOOD TO
KNOW HER HOLINESS
IS TAKING THIS SO SERIOUSLY.
- BE CAREFUL WHAT YOU SAY, JEDA.
- OH, EXCUSE ME.
ALL HAIL THE MIGHTY PRINCESS.
YOU'RE SUCH A
LOYAL SLAVE, VARGAS.
- WHERE ARE YOU GOING?
- WE'RE WASTING OUR TIME HERE.
BUT BY ALL MEANS,
LET THE MISTRESS ENJOY HER BATH.
- WHO GOES THERE?
- ( monkey chattering )
- I SAID WHO GOES THERE?
- IT'S A MONKEY.
- ( gasps ) LOOK OUT, PRINCESS!
IT MIGHT BE DANGEROUS!
- GET OUT OF THERE! IMMEDIATELY!
- IT'S OKAY.
- COME ON! QUICKLY!
- CUTE MONKEY.
- NO ONE EVER LISTENS.
- HERE WE ARE.
GO.
GOOD WORK.
- I WONDER WHERE JEDA WENT.
- I DON'T LIKE JEDA.
HE'S NEVER EVEN PLAYED WITH
ME ONCE. I DON'T LIKE HIM.
- IT'S NO USE TAKING IT
PERSONALLY, MISTRESS.
IT'S JUST THE WAY HE IS.
- I'M FINISHED, MONKEY,
GIVE THE EARS BACK.
- HEY! RETURN THE
PRINCESS' CAT EARS!
- DON'T LIKE THE BAD MONKEY.
- I TOLD YOU
YOU'D NEED A JACKET.
- I'M OKAY.
- REALLY? THEN YOU
DON'T WANT THIS?
- Hikaru: I WISH I COULD HEAR
WHAT THEY'RE SAYING.
THE SOUND OF THE WATER'S
TOO LOUD. LET'S GET CLOSER.
OKAY, KAORU?
- ( mewing )
- WHAT'S WRONG, HAZ?
- NOTHING.
- IS IT KAORU? YOU KNOW YOU
SHOULDN'T LET THAT GET TO YOU.
- KAORU DOESN'T
BOTHER ME AT ALL.
- OH, IS THAT RIGHT?
THEN WAS WITH THE TANTRUM?
- OKAY, FINE. MAYBE SHE
BOTHERS ME JUST A LITTLE BIT.
AFTER ALL, SHE'S YOUR FIANCEE.
- HOW MANY TIMES DO I HAVE TO
TELL YOU? THAT'S A TOTAL JOKE.
IT MEANS NOTHING.
OUR FAMILY DECIDED THAT.
- IF IT'S SO OBVIOUSLY NOTHING,
WHY DON'T YOU TELL HER THAT.
- I HONESTLY DON'T UNDERSTAND
WHAT THIS FIGHT IS ABOUT.
I'M DOING ALL THIS TRAINING
FOR YOU, AREN'T I?
SO I CAN KEEP YOU SAFE.
- I KNOW, BUT...
- FOR YOU.
AND MAYBE A LITTLE BIT FOR
GRANDPA AND ELFRIEDE, TOO.
- YEAH, I MISS THEM, TOO.
- IT'S HARD WHEN
I THINK ABOUT THEM.
BUT I CAN'T LET IT
HOLD ME BACK FOREVER.
WE'RE JUST GONNA HAVE
TO DO WHATEVER WE CAN
TO MOVE FORWARD, KID, OKAY?
- YEAH, OKAY.
- SURE, WE'VE GOT OUR PROBLEMS,
BUT LATELY THINGS
JUST SEEM DIFFERENT.
I FEEL LIKE I'M
BEHIND THE WHEEL,
LIKE WHAT I DO REALLY
MATTERS, YA KNOW?
- ( chuckles )
WELL, LISTEN TO MR. CONFIDENCE.
YOU DON'T SOUND LIKE
YOURSELF AT ALL, KOUHEI.
- OH, GEE, THANKS A LOT.
- REALLY. IT'S KINDA NICE.
- KAORU?
HEY. YOU DROPPED THIS.
- THANK YOU, SISTER.
I WAS THINKING, MAYBE NEXT
TIME I'LL ADD WHISKERS, TOO.
- THANKS FOR THE WARM
WELCOME, STRANGER.
- IT TAKES CONSIDERABLE SKILL
TO BREAK THE MIDO BARRIER.
- YOU HONOR ME, SIR.
I AM JEDA, THE PUPPET MASTER.
AND WHO ARE YOU?
- I WON'T WASTE MY NAME
ON VAMPIRE EARS.
- NO WAY!
- I DON'T SUPPOSE
YOU'D BE WILLING
TO SURRENDER MISTRESS LUNA?
I'D RATHER NOT KILL
ANYONE I DON'T HAVE TO.
- I KNOW NO GIRL BY THAT NAME.
- THAT'S TOO BAD.
- SO IT SEEMS.
- THEN LET'S BEGIN.
( grunting )
THERE'S NO ESCAPING.
I'LL FIND YOU NO
MATTER WHERE YOU RUN.
RESIGN YOURSELF TO DIE.
- RESIGN YOURSELF TO
SHUTTING YOUR ICKY FACE!
- PESKY LITTLE DEMON!
- CARELESSNESS IS
THE GREATEST FOE.
CAUGHT IN YOUR OWN FOUL WEB.
- MOVED TO THE BASE OF
THE MOUNTAIN?
TO DO THIS TO
SOMEONE OF MY TALENTS.
WELL, THIS IS GETTING
MORE INTERESTING.
- SEE YOU IN A MONTH, OKAY?
OH, AND GIRLS? PLEASE, FOR
ME, WATCH OUT FOR HER.
- FINE.
- 'KAY.
NEXT TIME I VISIT YOU I'LL HAVE
WHISKERS, TOO, BROTHER KOUHEI.
- WHEN I'M DONE TRAINING,
THEN I'LL EAT RICE.
- ( Hazuki gasps )
- NOW WHAT'S WRONG?
- I FORGOT SOMETHING.
I'LL BE RIGHT BACK.
- HUH? HAZUKI, WAIT!
- MAN, THIS IS LIKE
EATING CARDBOARD.
OH, WELL. YOU CAN'T
BE SELF-SUFFICIENT
IF YOU'RE LETTING SOMEONE
FEED YOU, RIGHT?
- KOUHEI!
- HAZUKI! HEY, UH, WHAT'RE
YOU DOING BACK SO SOON, HUH?
THIS ISN'T MY DINNER,
BY THE WAY. NO.
IT'S JUST A LITTLE SNACK,
THAT'S ALL!
YOU OKAY?
- ( crying ) NO...
- HEY, COME ON.
IT'S HARD THAT'S WHAT
THIS IS ABOUT, RIGHT?
LISTEN, KIDDO, I KNOW.
IT'S HARD FOR ME TOO.
I JUST HAVE TO FINISH TRAINING
AND THEN I'LL BE BACK.
- BUT WHEN? HOW LONG?
- IT'S HARD TO SAY.
BUT YOU REMEMBER MY PROMISE.
I'M DOING MY BEST SO I CAN GET
BACK TO YOU AS SOON AS I CAN.
YOU JUST HAVE TO
BE PATIENT, OKAY?
- I DON'T WANNA BE.
- WE'RE GONNA BE ALL RIGHT, HAZ.
- WELL? DID YOU GET
WHAT YOU FORGOT?
- YEAH.
- IT SURE FEELS EMPTY IN HERE.
- KOUHEI...
- LET'S CALL IT A DAY, PRINCESS.
- LUNA.
- ( theme song playing )
- ( singing in Japanese )
- ♪ JUST FOR MY LOVE ♪
♪ CAN'T STOP LOVING YOU ♪
♪ JUST FOR MY LOVE ♪
- Hazuki: OKAY, BIG BROTHER,
LET'S SHAKE THINGS UP A BIT.
HOW ABOUT A SUMO MATCH?
READY, AND GO!
FULL, FULL, FULL MOON!
NEXT TIME ON
MOON PHASE, EPISODE 20,
"GRANDFATHER, WHY ARE YOU
DRESSED LIKE THAT?"
AND THE WINNER IS... ME!
GOOD NIGHT, BIG BROTHER!