- ( people chattering )
- All: ITADAKIMASU!
- ELFRIEDE, MY DEAR, WILL YOU
PASS ME SOME OF THAT SOY SAUCE?
- WHY, OF COURSE,
RYUUHEI DARLING.
- IS THIS A JOKE?
- WHAT?
- WELL, YOU ARE THE ONE THAT
FIXED BREAKFAST THIS
MORNING, AREN'T YOU?
- YEAH, THAT'S RIGHT. YOU MAD
AT ME FOR FEEDING YOU NOW?
- I GUESS IT'S AN ACCIDENT THAT
MY FISH IS THE SIZE
OF MY PINKY THEN, HUH?
AND YOURS IS AS BIG
AS YOUR DEMON FACE?
- THEY'RE THE SAME SIZE.
- DON'T GIVE ME THAT. I'VE SEEN
EYELASHES BIGGER THAN THIS.
- IT JUST LOOKS SMALL
IN YOUR MAN HANDS.
- ( Hikaru gasping )
- WOULD YOU TWO KNOCK IT OFF
ALREADY? IT'S WAY TOO EARLY.
- ( softly ) I THINK MINE'S ONLY
BEEN COOKED HALFWAY THROUGH.
- SWAP YOUR FISH
WITH KAORU'S, FREAK-O.
- NO WAY.
- IT'S NOT A REQUEST.
- N-O.
- SWAP IT NOW!
- NO!
- COME ON,
I'M TRYING TO EAT.
- ( both grunting )
- DO YOU THINK I COULD
HAVE A SECOND HELPING,
ELFRIEDE DEAREST?
- SURE, RYUUHEI HONEY.
- ( Haiji exclaiming )
- YEAH, IT DEFINITELY TASTES
LIKE IT'S RAW IN THE MIDDLE.
- ELFRIEDE, MY SWEET,
I'D LOVE SOME MORE SOUP, TOO,
IF IT'S NOT TOO MUCH TROUBLE.
- NO. NOT AT ALL.
- ( gasping )
- WHAT THE...
- HIS SWEET?
- ( chuckles )
IS SOMETHING WRONG?
- HAVEN'T YOU HEARD THE THINGS
THEY'VE BEEN SAYING?
"HONEY" THIS, "DEAREST" THAT.
- YEAH. NEXT THING YOU KNOW
SHE'LL START CALLING HIM
"PEAS AND CARROTS."
- YEAH, IT SOUNDS NICE.
THEY'RE JUST TERMS OF ENDEARMENT
AND MAYBE IF YOU GUYS USED THEM,
YOU WOULDN'T ARGUE SO MUCH.
- YOU'RE TOTALLY
MISSING THE POINT.
- YEAH, NUMB SKULL.
- WELL, MAYBE IF I JUST CLOSE MY
EYES AND EAT IT REALLY QUICKLY.
- ( laughing )
- Arte: SHE STOPPED MOVING.
- Hazuki: NOT NOW, ARTE, OKAY?
YOU THINK SO?
- THE SIGNS DO
POINT THAT WAY.
- SCANDALOUS.
- WHAT IN THE WORLD
ARE YOU GUYS TALKING ABOUT?
- YOU WOULDN'T UNDERSTAND IT,
NUMB SKULL.
- WOULD YOU STOP
CALLING ME THAT?
I'M ASKING YOU
A PERFECTLY REASONABLE QUESTION.
- Hikaru: REASONABLE IF
YOU'RE A NUMB SKULL.
- Kouhei: THEN HERE'S A
QUESTION. HOW MUCH OF A BRAT
DO YOU HAVE TO BE BEFORE
I LOCK YOU IN THE BASEMENT?
- I CAN'T HEAR YOU.
- HEY. ARTE?
- WHERE'S SHE GOING?
- ( gurgling )
- LOOK. SHE'S DROWNING.
- ( exclaims ) GUYS, LOOK!
- WHAT HAPPENED?
- ( coughing )
DEATH BY FISH BROTH
IS THE WORST WAY TO GO.
- YOU GOOF. WHAT'RE YOU DOING
SWIMMING IN SOUP?
- DON'T SCOLD ME, SLAVE BOY.
IT'S NOT MY FAULT.
I WAS DROWNING
BECAUSE ARTE PUT ME THERE.
- ARTE DID?
- THEY'RE NO FUN.
- KINDA TAKES PLAYTIME A LITTLE
TOO FAR, DON'T YOU THINK?
- YOU COULD SAY THAT.
I'M GOING TO HAVE TO HAVE A
TALK WITH THAT GIRL TODAY.
- OH, DEAR, MISSED A PIECE.
- YES, SLOPPY OLD ME.
THANKS, SUGAR PLUM.
- YOU'RE WELCOME, HANDSOME.
- DID ANYONE ELSE SEE THAT?
- HOLD ON.
ARE YOU SAYING THEY'RE,
LIKE, MORE THAN FRIENDS?
- Both: NUMB SKULL!
- SCANDALOUS.
- BY THE WAY, WHERE'S SEIJI?
I HAVEN'T SEEN HIM THIS MORNING.
- I TOLD HIM BREAKFAST WAS
READY, BUT HE NEVER CAME DOWN.
- STILL IN THAT ROOM, HUH?
I TELL YOU, THAT BOY'S
JUST INCAPABLE OF ADAPTING.
- ( typing )
- IT'S BEEN SIX MONTHS NOW,
AND STILL NO SIGN OF RELIEF,
OR EXPLANATION
FOR THE STRANGE CIRCUMSTANCES
THAT HAVE BEFALLEN US.
HOW CAN THEY STAY SO CALM?
HOW CAN THEY SIT IN THIS HOUSE,
EATING THEIR MEALS,
LAUGHING AS ALWAYS?
I DON'T UNDERSTAND THEM ANYMORE.
AM I THE ONLY ONE
WHO'S KEPT HIS SANITY?
WHEN?
WHEN WILL
THIS BIZARRE ISOLATION END?
WHEN WILL OUR RESCUERS FIND US?
- ( intense music playing )
- ( waves crashing )
- TALK ABOUT RELAXING.
WHAT A DAY.
THE SKY IS BLUE.
THE SUN IS SHINING.
- ( gasping for breath )
- MY HELPLESS TWIN SISTER
IS DROWNING.
( exclaims ) KAORU!
ARE YOU ALL RIGHT, KAORU?
- YEAH. THANKS TO YOU.
- GOOD, THEN WE CAN MOVE ON.
WHAT WERE YOU THINKING
SWIMMING IN THESE?
DIDN'T YOU KNOW THEY'D SOAK UP
WATER AND SINK YOU?
- THEY'RE MY HOTTIE PAIR.
I HAVE DIFFERENT PAWS
BUT THOSE ARE MY HOTTIE ONES.
- THEY ARE?
- MEOW.
- YES, OF COURSE!
YOU LOOK TOTALLY HOT.
- MEOW?
- ( both laughing )
- Hikaru: YEAH.
- MEOW.
- AWW.
- WELL, I'M HEADING OUT,
HONEY BABY.
- GREAT. I'LL SEE YOU
WHEN YOU GET BACK, SWEETUMS.
- TRY TO CATCH AN OCTOPUS
THIS TIME, OKAY?
- ( shouting )
LET'S TRY THAT AGAIN
WITHOUT YOU RUINING IT, BOY!
OKAY. I'M HEADING OUT,
CUTIE DEAREST.
- ALL RIGHT, SEE YOU WHEN YOU
GET BACK, YOU BEAUTIFUL MAN.
- BUT, REALLY, FIND AN OCTOPUS.
I'M GETTING TIRED OF FISH.
- SHUT YOUR MOUTH, BOY!
TAKE CARE.
- YOU, TOO.
- ( whistling )
- GOODBYE, DEAR.
HAVE A NICE HUNT.
- WHAT WAS THAT ABOUT?
- YOU REALLY SHOULDN'T HAVE
BROUGHT THAT UP, KOUHEI.
MENTIONING OCTOPUS.
DON'T YOU KNOW WHAT YOUR DEAR
GRANDFATHER HAS BEEN THROUGH?
HE'S TRIED VERY HARD
TO PUT THAT ALL BEHIND HIM.
- GRAMPS AND OCTOPUS?
NEVER HEARD OF THAT ONE.
- IT WAS HORRIFYING.
A TALE SO HAUNTING, FEW MEN
CAN EVEN BEAR TO HEAR IT.
IT HAPPENED 44 YEARS AGO,
IN A SEA MUCH LIKE THIS ONE.
HE SWAM THROUGH THE CAVE,
TENTACLES LASHING.
DEEPER INTO HIS BRAIN,
ATTACKING HIM WITH THE MEMORIES
OF THE GHOSTLY WOMAN
DRENCHED IN BLOOD.
- ( Kouhei screaming )
- AND THAT'S WHAT THEY SAY
HAPPENED 44 YEARS AGO.
- POOR GRANDPA. THAT'S TERRIBLE.
I DIDN'T EVEN KNOW
THEIR TENTACLES COULD DO THAT.
I'LL NEVER EAT
AN OCTOPUS AGAIN!
- Hazuki: OPEN THIS DOOR
RIGHT NOW, ARTE!
YOU'RE GONNA APOLOGIZE TO HAIJI
FOR WHAT YOU DID TO HER.
- Haiji: I'VE ALREADY
TRIED KNOCKING.
SHE REFUSES TO COME OUT.
- ( grumbling ) LET'S GO!
- WHAT DO YOU MEAN, MASTER?
DON'T GIVE UP NOW!
- I'M NOT GIVING UP.
I'M JUST NOT LETTING HER
WASTE ANY MORE OF MY TIME.
SHE DIDN'T EAT MUCH AT BREAKFAST
SO SHE'S BOUND TO COME OUT SOON.
- BUT, MASTER...
- I SAID, LET'S GO!
WE'LL YELL AT HER LATER.
- FINE.
- Seiji: SUDDENLY,
A THOUGHT OCCURRED TO ME.
DISTURBING IN ITS IMPLICATIONS.
HOW LONG CAN THIS HOUSE STAY
AFLOAT IN THESE UNKNOWN WATERS?
WHEN THE STORMS AND
THE HIGH WAVES COME,
WILL THIS HOUSE WITHSTAND THEM?
AFTER ALL,
IT'S JUST AN ORDINARY BUILDING.
WAIT A MINUTE.
HOW IN THE WORLD IS THIS HOUSE
STAYING AFLOAT RIGHT NOW?
- ( sighs )
IT SURE IS HOT, THOUGH.
HAIJI! CAN YOU BRING SOME JUICE?
HAIJI?
THAT'S WEIRD. SHE'S GONE.
- HAZUKI, THERE YOU ARE.
- OH, HEY, HIKARU.
DO YOU KNOW WHERE HAIJI WENT?
- YOU'D BETTER COME DOWNSTAIRS.
- WHY, DID SOMETHING HAPPEN?
- JUST COME SEE
FOR YOURSELF, OKAY?
- WELL, WELL.
LOOK WHO'S HERE.
SO, PRINCESS SOUP TORTURER
FINALLY COMES OUT OF HER ROOM.
WELL, IF YOU THINK WE FORGOT
WHAT YOU DID, YOU'RE WRONG!
ARTE! SORRY TO ASK, BUT WILL
YOU GO FIND HAIJI FOR ME?
YOU'RE GONNA APOLOGIZE,
UNDERSTOOD?
- ACTUALLY, THAT'S WHY
I BROUGHT YOU DOWN HERE.
- WHAT? WHAT IS IT?
- THERE'S A BITE.
- HAZUKI! REEL IT IN,
REEL IT IN NOW!
- WHY? WHO CARES?
- JUST DO IT, OKAY?
- OKAY. CALM DOWN.
HAIJI!
- OUCHIE, OUCHIE, OUCHIE.
- THAT'S A BIG ONE.
- SAY SOMETHING, HAIJI.
ARE YOU OKAY?
- SHE LOOKS TERRIBLE!
- WE CAUGHT A YELLOW TAIL
- HAIJI? HAIJI, ARE YOU OKAY?
- TOGETHER. AND, IT'S BIG.
- SHOULD WE DO CPR OR SOMETHING?
- WE HAD FUN, DIDN'T WE?
- I NEVER LEARNED FIRST AID.
- AREN'T YOU PROUD OF ME, LUNA?
- SHAKE HER AT LEAST!
- THAT FISH WAS PRETTY BIG.
DO YOU THINK SHE
HAS A BROKEN BONE?
- Hikaru: WAIT, I THINK I SAW
HER BLINK. DID YOU SEE THAT?
- HOLD ON.
WHERE ARE YOU GOING?
ARTE! GET BACK HERE.
WHAT'S THAT GIRL'S PROBLEM?
SHE'S SUCH A BIG BRAT!
HONESTLY, I DON'T
UNDERSTAND HER AT ALL.
SEAWEED, HUH?
WHAT IN THE...
- I'M ONLY GUESSING, HAZ,
BUT MAYBE ARTE'S DOING ALL THIS
JUST TO GET YOUR ATTENTION.
- SERIOUSLY?
- IT'S A GUARANTEED WAY
TO GET NOTICED, ISN'T IT?
MAKING YOU MAD?
- I GUESS SO.
BUT WHO WANTS ATTENTION FROM
SOMEONE WHO'S MAD AT
YOU ALL THE TIME?
IF SHE WANTS TO HANG OUT,
WHY CAN'T SHE JUST ASK?
- MAYBE BECAUSE SHE'S A LOT
LIKE HER OLDER SISTER.
ARTE DOESN'T REALLY UNDERSTAND
HOW TO DEAL WITH PEOPLE YET.
AFTER ALL THOSE YEARS ALONE,
IT'S A LOT TO TAKE IN.
YOU WERE LIKE THAT
YOURSELF IN THE BEGINNING,
DON'T YOU REMEMBER?
NOW, I'M NOT SAYING THAT
TO EXCUSE WHAT SHE'S DONE.
I KNOW THAT SHE'S GONE
A LITTLE OVERBOARD.
- IT'S MORE THAN
A LITTLE, KOUHEI.
THE GIRL'S A FREAKING TERROR.
- ( chuckles )
JUST TRY TO PUT YOURSELF
IN HER SHOES, OKAY?
- YEAH, OKAY.
YOU'VE GOT A POINT.
I'LL TRY MY BEST.
SHE IS MY LITTLE SISTER,
AFTER ALL.
- OH, YEAH,
AND SPEAKING OF A TERROR.
- YEAH?
- ELFRIEDE TOLD ME
THE CRAZIEST STORY
ABOUT GRANDPA
WHEN HE WAS YOUNG.
- WHAT?
- IT HAPPENED 44 YEARS AGO...
- ( waves crashing )
- Hazuki: ( screaming )
AN OCTOPUS DID WHAT?
- Seiji: BLOOD OF ANCESTRY,
DESTINY OF BLOOD.
BLOOD OF ANCESTRY,
- I'VE BROUGHT YOU TEA,
BROTHER SEIJI.
I'LL JUST SET IT DOWN HERE.
AND YOU CAN GET IT
WHEN YOU WANT.
- BLOOD OF ANCESTRY,
DESTINY OF BLOOD.
BLOOD OF ANCESTRY,
- WHAT KIND OF SPELL
IS THAT?
- Kaoru: FATE THROUGH
SEVEN GENERATIONS.
- OH, YEAH, I'VE HEARD OF THAT.
IT'S SUPPOSED TO
TELL OUR FUTURE.
HE DOESN'T LOOK TOO GOOD.
- Ryuuhei: HEY, I'M HOME.
AND WE'VE GOT A VISITOR.
- ...DESTINY OF BLOOD.
- Woman: HOW'S MY FAVORITE
ODDBALL FAMILY?
- WHO IS THAT?
- BLOOD OF ANCESTRY...
THAT VOICE...
BUT HOW COULD THAT BE?
- Elfriede: THAT'S
QUITE A CATCH, DARLING.
- Ryuuhei: NEVER
COULD'VE DONE IT
WITHOUT THIS YOUNG LADY'S MOVES.
- Hiromi: OH, PLEASE. I JUST
HELPED HERD THEM IN A LITTLE.
- WOW, IT REALLY IS HER.
- SEE? WHAT DID I SAY, KOUHEI?
I KNEW I RECOGNIZED HER VOICE!
- HEY, GUYS, HOW'S IT GOING?
LONG TIME, NO SEE.
- HOW IN THE WORLD
DID YOU GET HERE, HIROMI?
- ( giggling )
SURE YOU WANNA KNOW?
- Ryuuhei: IT'LL BLOW YOUR MIND.
- I'LL TAKE MY CHANCES.
- YEAH! SHOW US, HIROMI, PLEASE?
- OKAY. FOLLOW ME.
- ( footsteps )
- HEY, SEIJI. YOU FINALLY
CAME OUT OF YOUR HOLE.
- I HEARD HIROMI'S VOICE.
WHERE IS SHE?
- UH...
- SHE LEFT. SHE HAD
A VERY BUSY SCHEDULE.
- YEAH, I'VE GOT TO ADMIT.
MY MIND IS BLOWN.
- I KNEW HIROMI WAS TALENTED,
BUT THAT TAKES THE CAKE.
- Seiji: WAIT!
- HEY, SEIJI.
- HIROMI. WHERE IS SHE?
- YOU JUST BARELY MISSED HER.
- YEAH. SHE JUST
WENT BACK HOME.
- HOME? HIROMI WENT HOME?
- YEAH, IS THERE A PROBLEM?
- PROBLEM?
- SEIJI, STOP IT!
- HIROMI SHOWS UP OUT OF NOWHERE
AND YOU LET HER LEAVE,
AND YOU ASK ME
IF THERE'S A PROBLEM?
- IT'S HARD FOR ME
TO RESPOND TO YOU
WHEN YOU'RE TRYING
TO CHOKE ME TO DEATH.
- WHAT HAS GOTTEN
INTO YOU, SEIJI?
CALM DOWN!
- HAZUKI'S RIGHT.
YOU'VE REALLY BEEN MAKING
A FOOL OF YOURSELF LATELY.
YOU NEED TO RELAX.
- WHAT IS WRONG WITH YOU FREAKS?
I'M NOT SURE WHERE HIROMI CAME
FROM OR HOW SHE GOT HERE.
BUT CLEARLY SHE CAME
FROM THE OUTSIDE WORLD.
WHICH MEANS YOU LET OUR BEST
CHANCE OF BEING SAVED GET AWAY.
WHY AM I THE ONLY
ONE IN THIS HOUSE
WHO SEEMS TO CARE
ABOUT GETTING RESCUED?
DON'T YOU WANT TO GET
BACK TO THE MAINLAND,
OR CARE HOW WE GOT HERE?
HAVE YOU GONE MAD?
- YOU REALLY SHOULDN'T
SCREAM LIKE THAT.
YOU'LL LOSE YOUR VOICE.
- THERE'S NO REASON TO WORRY.
I'M SURE HIROMI
WILL COME BACK SOON
AND YOU CAN TALK TO HER THEN.
- OR MAYBE KISS?
- I JUST CAN'T GET
THROUGH TO THEM.
WE'RE VICTIMS OF SOME
STRANGE PARANORMAL EVENT
AND THEY DON'T CARE.
( screams )
- SEIJI, WHERE'RE YOU GOING?
WHAT'S WRONG?
- "WHAT'S WRONG" IS RIGHT.
I THINK SOMEONE'S
BEEN DRINKING SALTWATER.
-HE'S NOT IN HERE, EITHER.
I WONDER WHERE SEIJI WENT.
- ( waves crashing )
- ( screaming )
THE HOUSE IS FLOODING!
- MASTER, THERE YOU ARE!
- WHAT HAPPENED?
- WE'VE BEEN UNCORKED.
- ARTE!
- SHE PULLED THE CORK
OUT OF THE FLOOR, AND NOW THE
HOUSE IS FILLING UP WITH WATER.
- WE'LL SINK!
- IT POPPED.
IT POPPED.
- WHY WOULD YOU DO THAT, HUH?
- IT POPPED.
- STOP SAYING THAT,
I KNOW THE CORK POPPED.
AND FUNNY SOUNDS ARE NO EXCUSE
FOR SINKING A HOUSE.
- HAZUKI, WHAT ON EARTH
DID YOU DO?
- HOW COULD YOU?
- WE'VE BEEN UNCORKED.
- WHAT WERE YOU THINKING?
YOU'RE GONNA GET US ALL KILLED!
- NO, YOU GUYS, IT WASN'T ME!
- UH-OH.
- "UH-OH" IS RIGHT, MISSY!
YOU REALLY THINK I'D BE SO...
- Hikaru: BE SO WHAT? STUPID?
- WELL, OF COURSE WE DO. YOU'RE
STANDING THERE HOLDING THE CORK.
- OKAY, FINE, I DID IT.
SO, WHAT?
- MASTER, WHAT ARE YOU SAYING?
- WHY WOULD YOU DO THAT, HAZUKI?
I DON'T KNOW,
BECAUSE I FELT LIKE IT.
IT MADE A FUNNY POPPING SOUND
AND IT WAS THE MOST FUN
I'VE HAD ALL WEEK.
- Hikaru: THAT'S THE DUMBEST
REASON I EVER HEARD.
- IT'S JUST A CORK. WHO CARES?
- I CARE, FREAK-O.
YOU'RE GONNA MAKE US ALL DROWN.
- THEN PLUG THE HOLE
WITH YOUR FACE.
- MASTER, WHY ARE YOU
DOING THIS?
- I KNOW YOU DIDN'T UNCORK IT.
I SAW IT MYSELF.
- STOP TRYING
TO COVER FOR ME, HAIJI!
- IT WAS ME, OKAY?
I LOVE THE SOUND.
POP. POP. POP.
- STOP SAYING "POP."
- ( creaking )
- ( all screaming )
- WATCH OUT!
- HONEY SNOOKUMS.
- ELFRIEDE, ARE YOU HURT?
- I'M FINE, HAZUKI,
IT'S JUST A LITTLE SCRATCH.
THE IMPORTANT THING IS
WE PUT THE CORK BACK
BEFORE IT'S TOO LATE.
- GIVE IT TO ME. QUICK.
- I'LL HELP, TOO.
- PLEASE BE CAREFUL.
THIS REALLY IS BAD.
- OF COURSE, IT'S BAD. WE'RE
ALL IN TROUBLE BECAUSE OF YOU.
- I'M SORRY.
- Ryuuhei: PUSH, KOUHEI!
WE'VE GOT TO MAKE IT SEAL.
- ALL RIGHT. HERE WE GO.
- ( popping )
- THEY STOPPED THE FLOODING.
- OH, THANK GOODNESS.
- SO, LET'S MAKE A NOTE
NOT TO DO THAT AGAIN, OKAY?
- Seiji: A MIRACLE.
IT'S REALLY THERE. MY EYES
WEREN'T PLAYING TRICKS ON ME.
WE'LL BE SAVED! HEY!
HEY! HEY!
IT'S NO GOOD.
THEY'RE TOO FAR AWAY.
IF ONLY I COULD
SEND THEM A SIGNAL.
OF COURSE!
- HOT DAY OUT IN THE OPEN SEA,
ISN'T IT?
- CERTAINLY IS, SIR.
- HARD TO WIPE SWEAT IN THESE
THINGS, DON'T YOU THINK?
- CERTAINLY DO, SIR.
- HUH? WHAT'S THAT?
- A DISTRESS SIGNAL. ADMIRAL,
SIR, YOU SHOULD HEAR THIS.
- WHAT'S THE MATTER NOW?
- AN S.O.S.
- HEY, LOOK OVER THERE.
- ( exclaims )
- ( giggles )
- OH, WOW. SHE'S SO LOVELY.
LOVELY. SHE MUST BE
ONE OF THE GREAT SIRENS OF MYTH.
NO MAN CAN RESIST HER.
- Officer 2: QUICK, COVER YOUR
EYES. PUT WAX IN YOUR EARS.
- WHY WOULD I? I LOVE HER!
- ME, TOO!
- DON'T LET HER GET AWAY, MEN.
AFTER HER, FULL THROTTLE.
- All: AYE AYE, SIR!
- Seiji: NO.
THEY'RE SAILING AWAY.
AND AT FULL SPEED.
BUT WHY? ( exclaims )
- HAZUKI.
- SCRUBBY DUBBY DINEY,
MAKE IT NICE AND SHINY,
SCRUBBY DUBBY CUPCAKES,
SCRUB IT TILL YOUR BACK ACHES,
SCRUBBY DUBBY DOLPHIN,
MASTER GOT THE RAW END.
( humming )
- YOU'RE HELPING?
- SORRY. I DIDN'T REALIZE.
I HAVE A SISTER
TO LOOK AFTER, TOO.
YOU'RE A GOOD SISTER, HAZUKI.
I KNOW YOU HAVEN'T
BEEN AT IT FOR LONG,
BUT I'D SAY
YOU'RE A NATURAL.
- YOU MEAN IT?
- HOW'S THAT CUT, ELFRIEDE?
FEEL BETTER?
- LIKE IT NEVER HAPPENED.
- I'M REALLY SORRY.
- DON'T BE. IT WAS AN ACCIDENT.
- Hazuki: ARTE.
- IT WASN'T HAZUKI.
I'M THE ONE
WHO TOOK OUT THE CORK.
- IT'S OKAY.
- WE'RE SAFE NOW. RIGHT?
- HAZUKI.
I'LL NEVER DO IT AGAIN.
I'LL NEVER PULL
THIS CORK OUT AGAIN.
- ( all gasping )
( all screaming )
- Seiji: I TOLD YOU, YOU FREAKS.
- SORRY, HAZUKI.
- OH, DON'T WORRY ABOUT IT,
WE'RE FINE.
( giggling nervously )
- ( whale singing )
- ( clears throat )
- ( giggles ) THE SHOW IS OVER.
- ( theme song playing )
- ( singing in Japanese )