- ( crackling )
- ( rattling )
- SOMEONE'S HERE.
- ( gasping )
- HELLO? IS ANYONE HOME?
HOW ON EARTH DOES
AN ENTIRE FAMILY
JUST DISAPPEAR WITHOUT A TRACE?
- JUST A HUMAN.
- Vargas: WHAT DO WE
DO WITH HER?
- Jeda: HOW 'BOUT DINNER?
- ( screaming )
- KOUHEI, KOUHEI, WHAT'S WRONG?
- PLEASE, I DON'T UNDERSTAND
WHAT'S HAPPENING!
STOP ACTING LIKE THIS!
- ( theme song playing )
( singing in Japanese )
- SO IT WASN'T JUST RYUUHEI'S
PLACE THAT WAS DESTROYED.
IT WAS THIS HOUSE TOO?
I DON'T UNDERSTAND.
- ( thinking ) WHERE DO I
KNOW HER FROM?
OH! SHE'S KOUHEI'S FRIEND!
- Vargas: HOW FORTUNATE.
A LITTLE SNACK.
- MONSTER!
JUST GET AWAY!
- NO. KOUHEI.
WHY ARE YOU SAYING THAT?
- ( breathing heavily )
- Yayoi: HAZUKI!
- Hazuki: PLEASE. HELP!
- THIS WILL BE
DIFFICULT TO HEAR.
KOUHEI'S JAGAN HAS MADE
HIM TERRIFIED OF YOU.
- ( gasping )
- Hazuki: "BIG BROTHER,
AM I THAT SCARY?"
- DON'T YOU EVEN THINK ABOUT
TOUCHING HER, FREAK!
I'LL SCREAM IF YOU DO.
- Vargas: OH, YOU CAN SCREAM
ALL YOU WANT, LITTLE GIRL.
SHE'S TOO FAR IN TO ESCAPE NOW.
- Arte: WHAT'S GOING ON?
- PRINCESS ARTE.
HUH?
DAMN IT!
- YOU'LL BE IN MAJOR TROUBLE
IF I KILL MYSELF.
YOU NEED ME AS A HOSTAGE.
- YOU THINK YOU CAN
BARGAIN WITH US?
- ( gasping )
- MAYBE THAT'S NOT A BAD IDEA.
YOU REALLY ARE ANNOYING ME.
- PRINCESS?
- IF YOU'RE IN A HURRY TO DIE,
I CAN HELP YOU.
- ( grunting )
- ( gasping )
- ( Jeda laughing )
HOW I'D LOVE TO SUCK YOUR BLOOD.
- ( whimpering )
- BIG BROTHER, YOU'RE NOT
ACTUALLY AFRAID OF ME, ARE YOU?
BUT YOU TOLD ME YOU DID ALL
OF THIS TO PROTECT ME!
- ( screaming )
- ( continues screaming )
( groans )
- I KNOW SOMETHING REALLY BAD IS
HAPPENING TO THEIR ENTIRE FAMILY
BUT I HAVE NO IDEA
HOW TO HELP THEM.
- ( clattering )
- PRINCESS, PLEASE UNDERSTAND.
WE NEED THIS GIRL ALIVE
IF WE WANT TO RETURN
MISTRESS LUNA TO OUR MASTER.
- WHAT A SAD STORY.
A LOVELY MEAL MISSED.
BECAUSE OF THE THREATS
OF THIS OBNOXIOUS GIRL.
- LET GO OF ME,
YOU DUMB VAMPIRE!
- TELL ME WHY YOU DID IT?
- DID WHAT, CREEP?
- WHY DID YOU GO OUT OF YOUR
WAY TO PROTECT HER?
- 'CAUSE SHE DOESN'T HAVE
ANYTHING TO DO WITH THIS, OKAY?
- THAT'S SO STUPID.
WASTING ALL YOUR TIME
CARING ABOUT OTHER PEOPLE.
YOU WOULDN'T UNDERSTAND...
YOU HEARTLESS BLOOD SUCKER!
- Yayoi: I USED MY KI
TO KNOCK HIM OUT.
HE SHOULD BE MORE
RELAXED WHEN HE WAKES.
- Hazuki: I DON'T UNDERSTAND.
WHAT'S HAPPENED TO HIM?
- I REMOVED THE SEAL THAT
SEPARATED KOUHEI FROM HIS JAGAN
EVER SINCE HE WAS A LITTLE BOY.
WITH HIS POWERS UNLOCKED,
HE HAS THE ABILITY TO SEE
THINGS NO ONE ELSE CAN.
AND SOMETHING HE SEES
IN YOU TERRIFIES HIM.
WE SUSPECT HE SEES WHAT
YOU MIGHT BECOME.
- ( gasping )
- THE LIFE OF A VAMPIRE
IS FILLED WITH EVIL,
SUFFERING, AND BLOOD.
YOU HAVE A TRAGIC PAST
AND A TERRIBLE DESTINY.
IF WE FAIL TO INTERVENE.
KOUHEI SEES THAT
WHEN HE LOOKS AT YOU.
- I'M NOT EVIL.
I'M NOT!
- SOME PART OF KOUHEI STILL
WANTS TO PROTECT YOU.
BUT BECAUSE OF WHAT
HE CAN SEE NOW,
YOU'VE BECOME
A MONSTER TO HIM.
HE FEARS YOU MORE THAN DEATH,
AND THAT FEAR MAKES HIM INSANE.
- I...
I'M SORRY. I DIDN'T KNOW
I HAD SUCH AN UGLY FATE.
( sobbing )
- Yayoi: I'M SORRY, HAZUKI.
THIS WILL NOT BE EASY FOR YOU.
- ( rustling )
- YEAH!
( chuckling )
I GOT 'EM!
- Koharu: SWEEPING ON
YOUR OWN, KAORU?
- ( Haiji screams )
- WHY ISN'T HAZUKI HELPING YOU?
- ( birds chirping )
- KOUHEI STILL HASN'T
SEEN THIS PLACE.
I'LL HAVE TO TAKE HIM
WHEN HE GETS BETTER.
I'VE NEVER SEEN HIS EYES
LOOK LIKE THAT BEFORE.
IT'S ALL MY STUPID FAULT.
I DID THIS TO HIM.
IF IT WEREN'T FOR ME,
HE'D BE FINE.
ALL HE'S EVER
DONE IS PROTECT ME
AND HELP ME AND TRY TO
BECOME STRONG FOR ME.
AND ALL I'VE EVER
DONE IS MAKE HIM SUFFER.
AND STILL, HE WAS ALWAYS
THERE FOR ME.
SORRY, KOUHEI.
- Woman: HAZUKI, DEAR.
THERE WILL COME A TIME WHEN
YOU WILL FIND SOMEONE
WHO YOU TRULY LOVE.
WHEN THAT DAY ARRIVES,
YOU MUST NOT SEAL THE
BLOOD PACT WITH HIM.
DO YOU UNDERSTAND?
NEVER WITH THE ONE YOU LOVE.
MOTHER, IS THIS WHAT YOU
WARNED ME ABOUT THEN?
- Seiji: THIS IS YOUR FAULT.
HE'S HERE BECAUSE OF YOU.
- HUMANS ARE SLAVES. ANIMALS.
LOWLY CREATURES PUT
HERE FOR OUR USE.
- NO, STOP IT!
- ( whimpering )
THE MONSTER THAT I SAW IN HERE
LAST NIGHT, THAT WAS HAZUKI.
BUT HOW COULD IT BE, MASTER?
I JUST DON'T UNDERSTAND
WHAT'S GOING ON ANYMORE.
IT'S LIKE I CAN'T THINK STRAIGHT
AND EVERYTHING THAT'S HAPPENING
IS ALL JUMBLED UP
INSIDE MY HEAD.
FROM THE FIRST MOMENT I SAW HER,
I COULDN'T FORGET HER.
I COULDN'T GET HER
OUT OF MY MIND.
SHE'S SO POWERFUL,
BUT FRAGILE TOO.
I WANNA PROTECT HER.
I... I DO!
BUT NOW I'M SEEING THINGS
LIKE I NEVER HAVE BEFORE.
THERE'RE THESE
SHADOWS AROUND HER
AND THEY'RE ALL
SCREAMING IN PAIN.
I THOUGHT THAT I WAS
READY FOR THIS.
I THOUGHT THAT I COULD FIGHT
THROUGH IT ALL BUT I JUST CAN'T!
I CAN'T!
( sobbing )
- ALL WHO POSSESS JAGAN
FACE THESE TERRORS, KOUHEI.
AS I WARNED YOU,
NO ONE IN OUR FAMILY HAS EVER
BEEN ABLE TO OVERCOME THEM.
BUT YOU ACCEPTED
YOUR POWER, KOUHEI.
YOU MUST NOW ACCEPT THIS
TERROR SO YOU CAN BEAT IT.
I WON'T PRETEND IT WILL BE EASY,
BUT THERE'S NO OTHER WAY.
REMEMBER YOUR TRAINING
AND USE IT.
I'LL TRY.
I WILL.
- IT'S RECKLESS TO UNLEASH
THIS POWER IN KOUHEI.
HE'S MORE LIKELY TO
HURT HIMSELF THAN AN ENEMY.
BUT I KNOW WE'LL
LOSE WITHOUT HIM.
AND BESIDES, I WOULD LIKE TO
SEE WHAT JAGAN CAN DO.
ALL OF THAT POWER,
IN ONE HALF-TRAINED AMATEUR.
- ( clattering )
- THIS "JAGAN" OF THEIRS MUST BE
SOMETHING VERY SPECIAL.
PERHAPS I SHOULDN'T WAIT
UNTIL THE NEXT FULL
MOON TO RETRIEVE HER.
- WHAT'RE YOU DOING?
- YOU KNOW, MR. VARGAS,
STANDING NEXT TO YOU
REALLY MAKES ME ILL.
- WHAT?
I'M AFRAID I'LL BE WORKING
ALONE FROM NOW ON.
- WHERE ARE YOU GOING?
- AWAY, PRINCESS. TRY NOT
TO SHED TOO MANY TEARS.
- YOU CAN'T DO THAT!
- YOU GO ON EARNING YOUR KEEP
BY PLAYING MOMMY TO THIS GIRL.
I HAVE OTHER WAYS
OF IMPRESSING OUR MASTER.
- YOU'RE A FOOL!
- THEY'RE SPLITTING UP, HUH?
- JEDA?
- YES?
- ( popping )
- THE WHOLE TIME WE
TRAVELED TOGETHER,
YOU NEVER PLAYED WITH ME ONCE.
- ( gasping )
- SORRY, PRINCESS.
YOU'LL HAVE TO MOVE
FASTER THAN THAT.
- ( clanging )
- ( gasping )
- Hikaru: SURE IS QUIET NOW.
- Arte: I DON'T NEED THAT DUMMY.
- Hikaru: NO?
- Arte: VARGAS AND I CAN
HANDLE THAT BRAT LUNA EASILY.
YOUR FRIEND LEFT YOU
AND YOU DON'T EVEN CARE.
YOU'RE FIGHTING
WITH YOUR SISTER.
IS THIS REALLY WHAT IT'S
LIKE TO BE A VAMPIRE?
IS THIS WHAT
IT'S ALL ABOUT?
NO ONE MATTERS BUT YOU,
NOT EVEN YOUR OWN FAMILY.
YOU'RE MEAN AND CRUEL AND
BEFORE LONG YOU'LL BE ALL ALONE.
BUT THAT DOESN'T MATTER
TO YOU EITHER, DOES IT?
- ( whistling )
- Arte: SOON.
- ( exploding )
- SOON I'LL MAKE SURE
LUNA'S ALL ALONE TOO.
- KOUHEI.
- Seiji: ALL THIS IS
YOUR FAULT, YOU KNOW.
YOUR SELFISHNESS HAS
ENDANGERED US ALL.
WE'VE ALL ENDED UP RISKING
OUR LIVES JUST TO PROTECT YOU.
BUT STILL WE'LL LOSE.
AND THEN WE'LL BE KILLED.
AND IT'LL BE YOUR FAULT.
- SEIJI, PLEASE.
- STOP PUTTING THIS
FAMILY IN DANGER, HAZUKI,
AND GO BACK TO YOUR OWN KIND.
- MY KIND?
- TO THOSE EVIL,
HEARTLESS VAMPIRES
WHO ACTUALLY
WANT YOU AROUND.
- ( gasping )
- BUT PLEASE, CAN'T
YOU TELL HOW
EVERYONE IN THIS HOUSE
IS HURTING RIGHT NOW?
- IT CAN'T BE HELPED.
- WILL YOU BE THE ONE TO
EXPLAIN THAT TO THE CHILDREN?
- THAT'S NOT FOR ME TO DO.
- YOU SAY THAT. YOU ACT
LIKE YOU'RE DETACHED.
AND YET, EVERY TIME
KOUHEI FEELS PAIN,
THIS AMULET DIGS INTO
YOUR CHEST ABOVE YOUR HEART.
SO WHILE YOU'RE MAKING
PLANS FROM THE SHADOWS,
ASK YOURSELF, IS THIS TRIAL
OF YOURS WORTH IT?
IF KOUHEI DOES FALL
APART FROM THIS,
AND IF HAZUKI LOSES HERSELF
AS SHE ONCE DID,
THEN WHAT WILL WE
HAVE LEFT TO SAVE?
- I'M GOING HOME NOW.
JUST LET ME GET PAST.
- SURELY YOU'VE REALIZED BY NOW
YOU'RE TOO DIFFERENT.
YOU COMING TO LIVE WITH US
WAS AN EXPERIMENT.
AND IT'S CLEAR TO
ALL OF US THAT IT'S FAILED.
- MOVE IT!
- FACE THE FACTS. YOU'LL
NEVER BE HUMAN, HAZUKI.
I'M JUST BEING HONEST
WITH YOU.
THERE'S SIMPLY NO PLACE FOR
A CREATURE LIKE
YOU IN OUR HOUSE.
YOU ARE NOT NEEDED
OR WANTED HERE.
THE OTHERS MAY PRETEND
TO PUT UP WITH YOU
TO SPARE YOUR FEELINGS,
BUT THE TRUTH IS YOU AREN'T
ACCEPTED BY ANY OF US.
WE WANT YOU OUT, HAZUKI.
IT'S TIME TO LEAVE.
- BUT, THAT CAN'T BE TRUE!
- AND WHY NOT?
- WHAT ABOUT WHAT
KOUHEI SAID TO ME?
- YOU'RE WHAT KEEPS ME GOING,
THROUGH ALL THE HARD STUFF.
- YOU JUST DON'T GET IT!
KOUHEI WANTS ME TO BE
WITH HIM. I KNOW HE DOES!
- TAKE A LOOK AT KOUHEI NOW,
HAZUKI. YOU HORRIFY HIM.
THE MERE SIGHT OF YOU
MAKES HIM SCREAM IN TERROR.
- BUT, NO!
THAT'S BECAUSE...
- BECAUSE HE SEES WHAT YOU ARE.
- ( sobbing )
- ( clanging )
- Yayoi: STOP IT, SEIJI!
KOUHEI WILL MASTER HIS JAGAN
AND OVERCOME HIS FEARS.
HE WILL OVERCOME THEM
BECAUSE HE HAS NO OTHER CHOICE.
AND WHEN HE DOES,
HE WILL WANT
HAZUKI WITH HIM.
- YOU REALLY THINK SO?
- ( clattering )
- THE THINGS THAT
YOU HAVE SUFFERED?
THE PAIN THAT KOUHEI IS
DEALING WITH NOW?
DID YOU KNOW THIS
WOULD HAPPEN?
- ( gasping )
- DID YOU FORESEE ALL THIS
FROM THE BEGINNING, OLD MAN?
- I THOUGHT I COULD HANDLE IT.
I DIDN'T KNOW HOW GREAT
HAZUKI'S BURDEN WAS.
- WE'VE MADE MISTAKES.
WE UNDERSTAND THAT.
BUT THERE'S NO TURNING BACK NOW.
ALL WE CAN DO IS TRY
TO FIND A WAY THROUGH.
- I HAVE THOUGHT
ABOUT USING THE POWER.
- BUT YOU CAN'T.
YOU KNOW IT COULD KILL YOU!
- THERE MAY BE NO OTHER WAY.
- IS THERE ANYTHING
WE CAN DO TO HELP?
- ( distant rumbling )
WHAT WAS THAT?
THE MAGIC BARRIER'S BEEN BROKEN!
- ( gasping )
HAIJI, STAY WITH KOUHEI.
MAKE SURE HE'S SAFE!
- WHAT ABOUT YOU?
- PLEASE, JUST GO!
- ( rumbling )
- ( Hazuki exclaiming )
- Yayoi: THE TREES
HAVE BEEN POSSESSED.
SUBMIT TO MY CONTROL!
- PLEASE ASSIST US, SPIRITS!
- NOT ENOUGH. HAZUKI,
WE NEED YOUR POWER NOW.
- ( gasping )
- YOU HAVE TO FEED.
- BUT, BUT, KOUHEI!
HE'S TERRIFIED OF ME.
- I TOLD HIM HE HAD
TO BEAT HIS FEAR.
HE MUST UNDERSTAND THAT.
HE HAS NO OTHER OPTIONS.
NOW GO TO HIM!
- RIGHT!
- LOOK OUT!
- WHO'S THERE?
- YOU HAVE TO HURRY!
- ( gasping )
- ( explosion )
- THIS IS OUR FIGHT NOW, TOO.
- WE'RE IN THIS WITH YOU, YAYOI.
- ( panting )
- Seiji: THE MERE SIGHT OF YOU
MAKES HIM SCREAM IN TERROR.
- Yayoi: KOUHEI WILL MASTER HIS
JAGAN AND OVERCOME HIS FEARS.
- PLEASE ACCEPT ME,
KOUHEI. PLEASE.
- WE'RE UNDER ATTACK!
WAKE UP, SLAVE!
- ( knock on door )
- ALL RIGHT, KOUHEI. GOTTA
PULL YOURSELF TOGETHER.
IT'S TIME. COME ON.
- DON'T YOU GET IT? WE CAN'T
DO THIS WITHOUT YOU!
GET OFF YOUR BUTT!
- I HAVE TO GO HELP THEM.
I HAVE TO DO MY PART!
GET UP, OR HAZUKI'S
GOING TO BE TAKEN!
- I NEED YOU.
- Jeda: I DON'T SEE
MISTRESS LUNA.
- ( all gasping )
- Yayoi: YOU AGAIN!
- THERE'S NO POINT IN RESISTING.
- SEIJI!
- IT WOULD'VE BEEN
SO MUCH EASIER
IF YOU HAD JUST
HANDED OVER THE GIRL.
- Ryuuhei: THIS VAMPIRE'S
POSSESSED HIM!
- HAZUKI, THIS IS IT!
- ( Kouhei screaming )
- BE STRONG, KOUHEI!
- THE VAMPIRES ARE HERE, KOUHEI.
MASTER YAYOI AND THE OTHERS
ARE TRYING TO FIGHT THEM OFF,
BUT IT'S NOT ENOUGH.
I'M HERE BECAUSE
I NEED TO KISS YOU.
KOUHEI!
- ( whimpering )
- ( screaming )
- WHY ARE YOU IN SO MUCH PAIN?
AM I REALLY SO TERRIBLE THAT
I SCARE YOU THIS MUCH, KOUHEI?
- ( screaming )
- ( grunting )
- OH, NO! ARE YOU OKAY?
- THIS HAS ALWAYS
BEEN A ONE-MAN JOB.
I NEVER NEEDED THAT
BUMBLING FOOL VARGAS
OR THE SNOTTY LITTLE PRINCESS.
THE MASTER WILL THANK ONLY ME!
MISTRESS LUNA!
RETURN PEACEFULLY
WITH ME TO YOUR MASTER,
AND I WON'T HAVE TO HURT
YOUR MISERABLE HUMAN PETS.
- THIS REALLY IS ALL MY FAULT.
( sobbing )
KOUHEI?
YOU REMEMBER THE
FIRST TIME WE MET?
I NEEDED YOU TO GET ME
OUT OF THAT CASTLE.
YOU WERE SO STUBBORN
AND FRUSTRATING,
AND SUCH A TERRIBLE SLAVE.
BUT YOU GOT ME OUT.
YOU HELPED ME LOOK
FOR MY MOTHER.
AND YOU GAVE ME A HOME.
YOU FOUGHT WITH ME,
AND TEASED ME,
AND MADE ME WANNA SLAP
YOUR BIG, STUPID HEAD,
BUT YOU WOULD
NEVER GAVE UP ON ME.
YOU GAVE ME THIS GREAT FAMILY
AND MADE ME REALIZE I DIDN'T
HAVE TO BE ALONE ANYMORE.
AND EVEN THOUGH I HAVEN'T
FOUND MY MOTHER,
IT HASN'T BEEN SO BAD.
BECAUSE I'VE HAD YOU ALL.
YOU GAVE ME THEM.
AND BECAUSE OF YOU,
THEY LEARNED TO ACCEPT ME
AND CARE ABOUT ME AND
TREAT ME LIKE ONE OF THEIR OWN.
NO MATTER HOW HARD THINGS GOT,
YOU WERE ALWAYS THERE
TO PROTECT ME,
AND COME RESCUE ME,
EVEN WHEN I WAS SO AWFUL
I DIDN'T DESERVE IT AT ALL.
YOU REFUSED TO GIVE UP ON ME!
THIS WOULD'VE BEEN A LOT EASIER
TO SAY IF I WAS A NORMAL GIRL.
I'M SURE I COULD'VE SAID IT
SOONER AND BETTER THAN THIS,
BUT I'LL SAY IT NOW.
THANKS FOR EVERYTHING.
AND I LOVE YOU, KOUHEI!
- ( sobbing )
- ( groaning )
- THIS IS FOR KOUHEI.
PLEASE GIVE IT TO HIM SINCE
I COULDN'T DO IT MYSELF.
- BUT, HAZUKI, WHAT DO YOU MEAN?
- YOU HAVE TO PROMISE NEVER
TO BOTHER THEM AGAIN.
I'LL GO WITH YOU NOW.
BACK TO "MY KIND."
- ( theme song playing )
( singing in Japanese )
- Hiromi: HELLO, BIG BROTHER!
TIME TO STOP SCREAMING
AND ANSWER A LITTLE RIDDLE.
EVEN YOU CAN FIGURE THIS ONE
OUT, I PROMISE. HERE GOES!
WHAT IS BLACK WHEN YOU BUY IT,
RED WHEN YOU USE IT, AND GRAY
WHEN YOU THROW IT AWAY?
DON'T TELL ME YOU'RE
GIVING UP ALREADY!
ALL RIGHT, I'LL TELL YOU.
FULL, FULL, FULL MOON!
THE ANSWER IS
CHARCOAL, DUMMY!
NEXT TIME ON MOON PHASE.
"GOOD-BYE BIG BROTHER...
I'M GOING BACK?
I'M REALLY GOING BACK?"
TRY TO SMARTEN UP
A BIT BY THEN, OKAY?