- I'VE HEARD SO MUCH
ABOUT YOU, MISTRESS LUNA.
IT'S TRULY AN HONOR.
- IS THAT SO? TOO BAD I CAN'T
SAY THE SAME THING ABOUT YOU.
- NOW, NOW, MISTRESS LUNA.
- WHY DO YOU KEEP CALLING ME
THAT? THAT'S NOT WHO I AM!
MY NAME IS HAZUKI!
- MY, MY. WHAT A STRANGE
SENSE OF HUMOR YOU HAVE.
YOU KNOW, I HAVE BEEN WATCHING
YOU, WAITING FOR THIS MOMENT.
WHEN YOU WOULD BATHE
IN THE FULL MOON
AND RETURN TO YOUR
TRUE SELF AGAIN.
SO HERE WE ARE.
YOU'VE HAD YOUR FUN.
IT'S TIME TO RETURN HOME TO
THE CASTLE, MISTRESS LUNA,
WHERE YOU BELONG.
- STOP CALLING ME THAT.
IT'S NOT MY NAME!
- YOU'RE SERIOUS, AREN'T YOU?
- OF COURSE I AM, YOU FREAK!
NOW, WHO ARE YOU?
- WHAT A TROUBLING SITUATION.
IS THERE ANY WAY YOU COULD
BRING LUNA OUT?
I REALLY NEED TO TALK TO HER.
- TELL ME YOUR NAME!
- FORGIVE ME, MY TERRIBLE
MANNERS. MY NAME IS ELFRIEDE.
I AM SERVANT TO THE STEWARD
OF SCHWARTZ QUELLE CASTLE.
COUNT KINKEL IS MY
MASTER'S NAME.
- ( gasps )
- AND IN ACCORDANCE WITH
MY MASTER'S WISHES,
I HAVE TRAVELED FROM GERMANY TO
BRING YOU HOME SAFELY, MISTRESS.
I HOPE YOU WILL RECOGNIZE
ME FROM NOW ON.
- ( theme song playing )
- ( singing in Japanese )
- OWIE, WELL, IF YOU'VE COME
TO TAKE ME BACK BY FORCE,
I PROMISE IT WON'T BE EASY.
I'M REALLY GOOD AT
KICKING AND SCREAMING.
- THAT'S NOT MY INTENTION
AT ALL, MISTRESS LUNA.
OUR WISH IS THAT YOU RETURN TO
THE CASTLE OF YOUR OWN VOLITION,
HAPPY AND UNBOUND.
I'VE COME TO EXPLAIN
THE MERITS OF THAT CHOICE.
I HOPE YOU'LL AGREE.
- OH, YOU DO, HUH?
WHAT IF I SAY NO?
- OH DEAR, I HADN'T
ENTERTAINED THAT POSSIBILITY.
IF YOU DON'T RETURN,
THAT MEANS I WON'T BE
ABLE TO FULFILL MY DUTY,
AND THE COUNT WILL BE
VERY UNHAPPY WITH ME.
- I'M AWFULLY SORRY
TO HEAR THAT, OKAY?
BUT I'M NOT STEPPING
FOOT IN THAT
DUMB, LONELY CASTLE
AGAIN, YOU UNDERSTAND?
TONIGHT OR EVER.
- ARE YOU SURE YOU
WANNA DO THIS, MISTRESS?
- WE'RE DONE HERE.
I'M NOT GOING BACK. GOODNIGHT.
TELL YOUR FRIEND TO WATCH WHERE
HE'S GOING. LITTLE PEST.
- ( squeaking )
- WHAT IS HE DOING?
WHAT THE...
- ( Haiji whimpers )
- ( clattering )
- (exclaims ) WHAT'S IT DOING?
HEY! THAT'S DANGEROUS!
WHOA! IT'S GONNA POKE
SOMEONE'S... HEY!
WHAT'S THE BIG IDEA?
- ( clattering continues )
- ( exclaiming )
THAT DIDN'T FEEL GOOD!
HEY, NO FAIR! I THOUGHT
YOU SAID IT WAS MY CHOICE!
WHAT AM I CHOOSING BETWEEN?
GOING WITH YOU AND
A HOLE IN MY HEAD?
- ( screaming )
- YOU'LL HAVE TO
FORGIVE ME, MY DEAR.
AS I SAID, CONVINCING YOU
WAS MY INTENTION,
BUT I THOUGHT I'D BE
SPEAKING TO MISTRESS LUNA,
WHO'D BE MORE OPEN TO REASON.
I'M AFRAID NOW I NEED TO ALTER
MY TACTICS TO BRING YOU HOME.
- IT'S SO LATE.
I WONDER WHAT
THOSE KIDS COULD BE
DOING OUT AT THIS TIME OF NIGHT.
NOTHING TOO HORRIBLY DANGEROUS,
I HOPE.
- ENOUGH IS ENOUGH.
LEAVE ME ALONE!
- REMARKABLE STRENGTH, MISTRESS,
BUT YOUR DELIVERY
NEEDS SOME WORK.
IT LACKS A CERTAIN ELEGANCE.
YOU KNOW, THE COUNT COULD
HELP YOU WITH THAT IF
YOU'RE NICE TO HIM.
- OH, SHUT UP.
LIKE YOU'RE ONE TO TALK!
YOU'RE USING A BALLED UP RAT
TO DO YOUR DIRTY WORK!
WHERE'S THE ELEGANCE IN THAT?
- INTERESTING POINT.
PERHAPS YOU'LL FIND THIS TO BE A
MORE RESPECTABLE SHOW OF POWER.
- HUH?
- ( roaring )
- ( screaming )
- SURE, I KNOW
THAT PART OF TOWN.
SO IT'S A SPREAD ON
OLD SWEET SHOPS, RIGHT?
- ( indistinct screaming )
- HEY, CAN I USE A CAMERAMAN
FRIEND OF MINE FOR THIS?
HE DOES AWESOME WORK!
GREAT. YOU'RE THE BEST!
I'LL BE IN TOUCH, OKAY?
FINALLY SOME REAL WORK!
KOUHEI'S GONNA BE SO EXCITED.
- ( monster growling )
- LEAVE ME ALONE.
- THOSE EYES... THAT POWER...
SHE DRANK THE BLOOD
OF HER SLAVE.
- ( panting )
YOU'RE TICKING ME OFF!
( exclaiming )
KOUHEI, NO!
- ( monster growls in pain )
- IT JUST DISINTEGRATED WHEN
IT GOT CLOSE TO KOUHEI.
KOUHEI?
- HAZUKI?
EXCUSE ME, MA'AM?
WOULD YOU LIKE TO DO
SOME MODELING WORK?
- YOU MORON!
- HEY, WHAT WAS THAT? I'M SORRY.
WHAT'S WRONG WITH YOU?
- WRONG WITH ME?
WHAT'S WRONG WITH YOU,
YOU HAIR-BRAINED IDIOT?
HOW COULD YOU BE FLIRTING
AT A TIME LIKE THIS?
- SINCE WHEN WAS I FLIRTING?
I JUST ASKED HER IF I COULD
TAKE HER PHOTOGRAPH.
I'M A PHOTOGRAPHER.
- WELL, AND ISN'T THAT
A CONVENIENT EXCUSE!
SO YOU USE THAT LINE
ON EVERY GIRL YOU MEET?
- NO, ACTUALLY.
ONLY ON THE ONES WHO
SEEM FIT FOR THE JOB.
AND PROFESSIONALLY SPEAKING,
SHE'S WAY HOTTER AND
MORE MATURE THAN YOU.
OH, YEAH, THAT'S REAL MATURE.
- YOUR BLOOD'S SO THIN
IT'S GIVEN YOU BRAIN DAMAGE!
NO WONDER I CAN'T GET
ANY STRENGTH FROM IT.
YOU IDIOT!
- WHAT?
WAIT A MINUTE, ARE YOU TELLING
ME YOU SUCKED MY BLOOD AGAIN?
- GOT ANY COMPLAINTS?
- LOTS OF 'EM!
YOU TOOK ADVANTAGE
OF ME WHILE I WAS ASLEEP!
- YOU'RE MY SLAVE!
I DO WHAT I WANT!
- I'M YOUR BODYGUARD!
- WELL YOU'RE DOING A FINE JOB!
HERE'S AN ENEMY
TRYING TO KIDNAP ME,
AND YOU'RE OFFERING
HER PRIVATE SESSIONS!
- STOP MAKING IT SOUND LIKE
THAT! IT'S FOR MY PORTFOLIO.
WAIT, DID YOU SAY "ENEMY"?
- THE VAMPIRE'S LOVER.
- DID YOU SAY SOMETHING?
- NO, NO. I'VE SIMPLY REALIZED
I HAVE MORE TO THINK ABOUT.
I'LL BE LEAVING NOW.
- WHAT?
- ( exclaims in shock )
- HOLD ON. FIRST YOU SAY
YOU WANT TO TALK,
THEN YOU ATTACK,
THEN YOU LEAVE FOR NO REASON?
- ON THE CONTRARY, MISTRESS.
REASON DICTATES MY
ACTIONS ABOVE ALL.
I'LL RETURN IN A FEW DAYS TO
PRESENT A MORE
CONVINCING ARGUMENT.
I HOPE YOU'LL TAKE THIS CHANCE
TO CONTEMPLATE YOUR CHOICES,
AND THEIR EFFECTS.
MAY THE DARK OF NIGHT
PROTECT YOU, IN THE MEAN TIME.
- SO, THAT WOMAN, SHE WAS
ONE OF YOUR KIND, RIGHT?
- YEAH, I'M PRETTY SURE.
I CAN'T BELIEVE THIS.
I HAVEN'T EVEN HEARD
FROM MY MOTHER YET,
AND THEY'VE ALREADY
TRACKED ME DOWN.
WHAT SHOULD I DO?
- HEY, DON'T WORRY.
SHE JUST SAID SHE WANTED
TO CONVINCE YOU, RIGHT?
SO JUST KEEP SAYING NO.
- ( sighs ) THAT IS
WHAT SHE SAID.
BUT STILL, I DON'T KNOW.
WHY DO I FEEL SO TIRED, KOUHEI?
I KISSED YOU. I SHOULD HAVE MORE
ENERGY AFTER DRINKING BLOOD.
- HEY. LOOK AT ME, WILL YA?
YEAH, I NOTICED IT THE
FIRST TIME WE MET, TOO.
YOUR EYES TURN KINDA RED.
- DON'T SAY THAT.
I DON'T WANNA KNOW!
NOW WHAT? WHAT ARE YOU DOING?
- YOU SAID YOU'RE REALLY TIRED,
RIGHT? WELL, HOP ON.
A CAB RIDE IS WAY TOO EXPENSIVE.
THIS IS THE BEST I CAN DO.
- WHAT, YOU WANNA GIVE
ME A PIGGY-BACK RIDE,
LIKE I'M SOME LITTLE KID?
- JUST GET ON, OKAY?
- YOU DON'T HAVE TO ACT
LIKE MY BABYSITTER.
YOU'RE MY SLAVE, AND THAT'S IT!
YOU'RE ONLY CARRYING ME
BECAUSE THAT'S WHAT SLAVES DO.
UNDERSTOOD?
- YES, SIR, MASTER, SIR.
- DON'T GET AN ATTITUDE.
SAY "YES" LIKE YOU MEAN IT!
- "YES LIKE YOU MEAN IT!"
- KOUHEI, DUMMY! SAY YES!
- YES!
- BRATTY SMART ALECK!
- YOU'RE THE WORST SLAVE EVER!
- I CAN'T BREATHE!
- HAZUKI?
NEVER MIND.
- COME ON, LET'S GO!
- LAST ONE THERE
- GETS THE GROSS CANDY!
- WAIT UP, GUYS!
- ( camera clicking )
- ( all gasping )
- PRETTY COOL, HUH?
- I WANNA PICTURE OF THAT!
- TAKE MY PICTURE!
- NO WAY, ME FIRST!
- I'LL RETURN IN A FEW DAYS
TO PRESENT A MORE
CONVINCING ARGUMENT.
I HOPE YOU'LL TAKE THIS CHANCE
TO CONTEMPLATE YOUR CHOICES,
AND THEIR EFFECTS.
- ( yawns )
IT'D TAKE ONE HECK
OF AN ARGUMENT TO
CONVINCE HAZUKI TO GO BACK.
OH WELL, GUESS WE'LL
SEE SOON ENOUGH.
- Children: PRETTY PLEASE,
WOULD YOU TAKE OUR PICTURE?
- WHY DON'T YOU PLAY
THE QUIET GAME NOW?
- WELL, THE NEXT TIME WE GET A
CALL FROM HAUNTED CANDY MONTHLY,
WE'LL BE SET!
- IT HAPPENED AGAIN?
- OH WELL, IT'S
NOT A TOTAL WASTE.
WE'LL RUN THESE
IN OUR MAGAZINE.
I JUST DON'T UNDERSTAND IT.
GHOSTS IN A CANDY SHOP?
- WHAT CAN I SAY? IT'S A GIFT.
- I'LL JUST CALL THE CLIENT
AND TELL 'EM THERE WAS
A TECHNICAL MALFUNCTION.
AND IF I GET ANY MORE
ASSIGNMENTS I CAN PASS YOUR WAY,
I'LL LET YA KNOW.
I'M NOT GIVING UP ON YOU YET.
- THANK YOU. YOU'RE A LIFESAVER.
- OH, I ALMOST FORGOT.
I'VE GOT A LITTLE PRESENT
TO GIVE YOU, KOUHEI.
- A PRESENT?
- FOR YOUR GIRLFRIEND.
- DARN IT.
THAT STUPID KOUHEI.
TREATING ME LIKE A LITTLE KID
WHEN HE'S SUPPOSED
TO BE MY SLAVE.
- Kouhei: NO, ACTUALLY.
ONLY ON THE ONES WHO
SEEM FIT FOR THE JOB.
AND PROFESSIONALLY SPEAKING,
SHE'S WAY HOTTER AND
MORE MATURE THAN YOU.
- LIKE I CARE!
- WHO IS HE, MISTRESS LUNA?
YOU DRANK FROM HIS NECK,
YET SOMEHOW, HE DIDN'T
BECOME YOUR SLAVE.
AND THAT POWER THAT
ENCIRCLED HIM... WHAT WAS IT?
WITH WHOM HAVE YOU ALLIED?
- Ryuuhei: IN OTHER WORDS,
KOUHEI IS SO SPIRITUALLY INEPT,
SO COMPLETELY BLIND TO
ANYTHING SUPERNATURAL,
THAT THE DEMONIC MESSENGER'S
POWERS HAD AN OPPOSITE EFFECT.
DESTROYING IT INSTEAD.
- I SEE.
SO THE DEMON'S ENERGY
JUST BACKFIRED.
IT WASN'T THAT BIG BROTHER HAD
SOME HIDDEN STRENGTH THAT
CAME OUT IN THE FIGHT?
- NOPE.
IN TERMS OF POWER,
KOUHEI SCORES A ZERO.
( laughs )
- I'D RATHER TALK ABOUT
SOMETHING ELSE NOW.
LIKE HOW LONELY AND
BORING THIS SHOP CAN BE
WHEN THERE AREN'T ANY CUSTOMERS.
- QUIET TIMES ARE IMPORTANT.
THEY GIVE US A CHANCE TO TAKE
STOCK AND CLEAR THE DUST.
- I GUESS SO.
- ( Haiji mewing )
- HAIJI. NO CAUSING MISCHIEF.
- ( knocking on door )
- HEY, OPEN THE DOOR! HURRY UP!
- WHO IS THAT?
- I THINK IT'S BIG BROTHER!
AND IT SOUNDS LIKE
HE'S IN TROUBLE.
- AH, THANK GOODNESS...
THESE' RE FOR YOU!
- ( Hazuki screams )
YOU NITWIT!
WHAT ARE YOU DOING?
WOW! I'VE BEEN WANTING
MORE CLOTHES!
YOU CAN ONLY RECYCLE
THE SAME OUTFIT SO MANY TIMES.
THESE ARE THE
COOLEST PRESENTS EVER
AND THERE ARE SO MANY OF 'EM.
- LEAVE IT TO ANOTHER GOOD
CITIZEN OF THE FEMALE RACE
TO NOTICE WHAT YA NEEDED.
HIROMI'S DEFINITELY A
CARD-CARRYING MEMBER.
- IS SOMETHING WRONG?
- MMM-MMM.
- HEY, COME ON,
WHAT'S THE MATTER?
YOU FIND SOMETHING
YOU DON'T LIKE IN THERE?
- IT'S MY STUFF. GO AWAY!
- WELL, I'M THE ONE WHO
BROUGHT IT OVER HERE.
JUST LET ME SEE WHAT IT IS.
- IT'S UNDERWEAR, OKAY!
- UNDER... DON'T SHOW ME THAT!
- I WASN'T GOING TO,
YOU NOSY IDIOT!
- ( Ryuuhei chuckles )
- NOW STOP STANDING
THERE STARING.
TAKE THESE THINGS UPSTAIRS.
- HUH? WHY DO I HAVE TO?
- JUST SHUT UP AND GO!
- THANKS FOR THE HELP.
OUCH. DUMB BAGS DON'T FIT!
- ( mewing )
- WHAT, MY FRIEND?
IS SOMETHING WRONG?
POOR THING. YOU CAN'T EVEN
TALK IN THAT FORM, CAN YOU?
AH, WE HAVE A GUEST.
I MUST SAY,
THIS IS A RARE TREAT.
A YOUNG, BEAUTIFUL,
FOREIGN WOMAN,
FINDING HER WAY INTO A
JAPANESE ANTIQUE SHOP,
IN A QUIET PART OF TOWN.
- DO YOU FIND THAT PECULIAR?
- OH, NOT AT ALL. ANTIQUES
WITHSTAND THE TEST OF TIME.
IF THERE WASN'T SOMETHING ABOUT
THEM THAT COULD CAPTURE HEARTS
FROM ONE GENERATION TO THE NEXT,
THEN THEY NEVER
WOULD'VE SURVIVED.
- YES. I WOULD
CERTAINLY AGREE.
TRUE BEAUTY SHOULD
TRANSCEND CULTURE
AND FASCINATE ANY
EYES THAT SEE IT.
- WELL, YOU HAVE
DISCRIMINATING TASTE.
THAT'S AN EARLY 17TH CENTURY
IMARI WARE YOU'RE HOLDING.
ITS UNIQUE TEXTURE
AND ARABESQUE DESIGN
MAKE IT QUITE POPULAR AMONG
THE MOST EDUCATED COLLECTORS.
- OH? I HAD NO IDEA.
- IF YOU'RE A FAN OF
THE IMARI STYLE, MADAM,
THERE IS ANOTHER MORE
SUBSTANTIAL PIECE
I'VE RECENTLY
GOTTEN MY HANDS ON.
WOULD YOU LIKE TO SEE?
- WHY YES, THANK YOU.
OH, MY.
YOU DO KNOW HOW
TO MAKE A GIRL SMILE.
- ( laughing )
- GRANDFATHER, I DIDN'T KNOW
WE HAD A CUSTOMER.
HELLO! WELCOME TO OUR...
- WELL! HI.
- ( Hazuki screams )
WHY ARE YOU HERE?
- WHY DO YOU THINK?
AS PROMISED, I'VE COME
TO SEE YOU AGAIN,
LITTLE ONE, SO WE
CAN FINISH OUR CHAT.
- IT'S ALREADY FINISHED.
I SAID I'M NOT GOING BACK!
- NOW, NOW, MY DEAR,
DON'T THROW A TANTRUM.
WITHOUT A TRANQUIL MIND
AND A POSITIVE OUTLOOK,
HOW WILL WE EVER HAVE
A MEANINGFUL DISCUSSION?
- THERE'S NOTHING TO DISCUSS,
YOU JERK!
- GEEZ, HAZUKI, SOUNDS
LIKE YOU'RE TALKING TO ME.
- AH! GOOD EVENING.
- OH, WHOA, IT'S YOU AGAIN. HI.
- DON'T SIT DOWN.
THIS IS JUST BETWEEN US.
- OH, ON THE CONTRARY,
THIS IS PERFECT TIMING.
I WAS HOPING I COULD
SPEAK TO YOU AS WELL.
- TO ME? ABOUT WHAT?
- THE MODELING WORK.
I'D BE DELIGHTED TO TRY IT.
- MODELING WORK?
- HUH?
- DON'T TELL ME
THAT YOU FORGOT.
- NO! THERE'S NO FORGETTING
HERE. I JUST UH... I DIDN'T...
LOOK, YOU'RE BEING
SERIOUS RIGHT?
YOU'RE NOT JUST
PULLING MY LEG?
- OH, I'M VERY SERIOUS.
IT'S SOMETHING I'VE NEVER DONE,
AND THERE'S SO MUCH
I'M CURIOUS ABOUT.
LIKE, WHAT SORT OF POSES
WOULD YOU WANT ME TO TAKE?
AND BESIDES,
ON A MORE PERSONAL LEVEL, I FIND
YOU IRRESISTIBLY FASCINATING.
- ( giggling )
- ( Hazuki grunts )
WHAT'S WRONG WITH YOU?
YOU CAN'T COME IN HERE AND
START FLIRTING WITH MY SLAVE.
HE'S NOT COMMUNAL PROPERTY.
- ( laughing ) YOU'RE SO FUNNY!
- WHAT ARE YOU LAUGHING
ABOUT NOW, HUH?
- FORGIVE ME,
I DON'T MEAN TO BE RUDE.
IT'S JUST THAT THE COUNT
TOLD ME ABOUT YOU,
AND HOW HEADSTRONG
YOU COULD BE,
BUT I THOUGHT HE WAS
TRYING TO KEEP ME FOCUSED.
I DIDN'T REALIZE HE WAS SERIOUS.
- OH, REALLY?
YOU CARE TO EXPLAIN THAT FOR ME?
- OH, YOU DON'T WANNA HEAR THIS.
- GO AHEAD. I CAN TAKE IT.
- YOU'LL BE ANGRY.
- YOU CAN'T SAY YOU KNOW STUFF
ABOUT ME THEN NOT SAY WHAT.
- FINE.
YOU'RE DELICATE, BUT RECKLESS
AND HOT-TEMPERED
AT THE SAME TIME.
YOU SEEM CONFIDENT AND DECISIVE,
BUT IN TRUTH YOU'RE
EASILY SCARED,
QUICK TO RUN FROM DIFFICULTY
WITHOUT CONCERN FOR REASON.
YOU'RE LIKE A CAT
WHO CLIMBS A TREE
THEN CAN'T FIND
HER WAY BACK DOWN.
- AND FURTHERMORE...
- THAT'S ENOUGH!
- REALLY? THERE'S
QUITE A BIT MORE.
- WELL, KEEP IT TO YOURSELF!
I'M NOT GONNA STAND HERE
WHILE YOU INSULT ME
JUST 'CAUSE YOU
MAKE IT SOUND SMART.
IS THAT THE ONLY REASON YOU
CAME HERE, TO HARASS ME?
- OH, NOT AT ALL, LITTLE ONE.
MY PURPOSE FOR COMING
HAS ALWAYS BEEN THE SAME.
TO BEG YOU, MISTRESS.
PLEASE RETURN TO THE CASTLE.
- ( grunting )
FOR THE LAST TIME.
GO AWAY!
GO AWAY! GO AWAY! GO AWAY!
- DEAR, YOU HAVE TO CALM DOWN.
YOU'RE THROWING
AN ABSOLUTE TANTRUM.
- GET OUT OF THIS HOUSE!
YOU GOLDEN-HAIRED EYESORE!
YOU RAT-WRANGLING,
POISON-TONGUED VAMPIRE WITCH!
I NEVER WANNA
SEE YOU AGAIN!
- THERE GOES THE
17TH CENTURY...
- ( Hazuki panting )
- HAVE YOU GOTTEN IT OUT
OF YOUR SYSTEM, MISTRESS?
OR IS THERE MORE?
- I'LL SHOW YOU MORE!
- HEY!
- I NEED TO SUCK
YOUR BLOOD AGAIN!
- GET OFF ME.
MY NECK'S NOT AN OPEN BAR.
- I'M GOING TO BEAT HER
SENSELESS! I NEED MORE ENERGY!
- WELL THEN DO SOME JUMPING
JACKS! DON'T SUCK MY BLOOD!
- KOUHEI, YOU DUMMY!
- NO MEANS NO. COME ON.
STOP BEING A LITTLE BRAT.
- ( door sliding open )
- I THINK IT'D BE BETTER
IF I LEFT NOW.
I'LL GIVE YOU A
CHANCE TO CALM DOWN,
AND WE CAN RESUME OUR
CONVERSATION ANOTHER TIME.
HAPPY NIGHTS UNTIL THEN.
- NEVER COME BACK AGAIN!
- UNBELIEVABLE.
- JUST SHUT UP AND
GET SOME SALT!
WE'RE GONNA PURIFY
THIS WHOLE HOUSE!
- SO, THERE REALLY ARE
VAMPIRES LIKE THAT.
I NEED TO HAVE A
LONG TALK WITH HER.
- Hazuki: WHY ARE YOU SUCH
A TERRIBLE SLAVE?
- Elfriede: KOUHEI MORIOKA.
I'M CERTAIN NOW.
EVEN THOUGH MISTRESS LUNA'S
TASTED YOUR BLOOD,
YOU ARE NOT HER SLAVE.
THERE'S ONLY ONE WHO
COULD WITHSTAND THE KISS.
YOU ARE THE VAMPIRE'S LOVER.
THE KEY TO CHANGING MY FATE.
- ( theme song playing )
- ( singing in Japanese )
- Hazuki: OKAY, BIG BROTHER.
IT'S RIDDLE TIME AGAIN,
WHO HAS BETTER STORIES TO TELL,
A MONKEY OR A CRAB?
NOW THINK ABOUT IT,
MONKEY OR CRAB?
FULL, FULL, FULL MOON!
TIME'S UP!
THE ANSWER IS, A MONKEY HAS
BETTER STORIES, OF COURSE.
CRABS DON'T HAVE TALES AT ALL.
NEXT TIME ON MOON PHASE,
IT'S "HEART THROBS IN KYOTO."
THAT SOUNDS LIKE FUN.
AND WAIT TILL YOU SEE
WHAT HAPPENS TO HAIJI.
OKAY, I'VE SAID ENOUGH.
GOODNIGHT, BIG BROTHER.