[reporter] The government
has begun to discuss the
emergency measures.
However, the mobilization of
Self‐Defense Forces has been the
subject of a frantic‐
[channel change]
10,000 have been victimized in
the Saitama area so far.
The governor has already called‐
[gunshot]
Already declared the state
of emergency and requested
emergency disaster relief...
[gunshots]
[reporter] It's a gunshot!
It looks like the police are
finally using firearms!
From what I can see, the‐
No, don't! No!
[screaming]
[concerned murmurs]
There appears to be a problem
with our remote.
[newscaster] From now on, we'll
bring you the story from inside
the studio.
The condition outside seem
extremely chaotic,
so stay home unless it's
absolutely necessary to
go outside.
We'll bring you more stories as
soon as it's safe to cover the
current situation from the site.
Is that all?
Why didn't they tell us
anything else?
[Saeko] They're afraid of
causing a panic.
A panic?
[Saya] Yeah you idiot.
First panic, then chaos,
and chaos causes a disruption
of order.
And then, when order
is disrupted,
well you should just hand it all
over to the walking corpses!
This unusal and unprecedented
biological phenomenon...
that spread throughout
North America...
has yet to be put
under control.
[reporter] Government
authorities have evacuated
the White House...
and will relocate to a command
center on board the aircraft
carrier George Washington.
There are reports that the
transfer of power is in
preparation...
for the use of tactical warheads
to combat the infestation.
We have currently lost
contact with Moscow.
Beijing has been set ablaze.
London has maintained order
while in Paris and Rome, there
are reports of looting.
The government officials
have declared a state of
Martial Law.
[becoming distorted]
Currently, the‐
[Takashi] So they're everywhere.
That's crazy...
Everything was normal when
I checked the internet
this morning.
[Rei] I can't believe this.
This happened all over the world
in a matter of a few hours.
[Rei] But they'll stop
it, right?
I mean they have to stop
it from spreading. I mean‐
Everything is going to back
to normal soon.
[Saya] That's not going
to happen.
[Takashi] Why do you have to
be so blunt about it?
This is a pandemic.
There's nothing we can do!
A pandemic?
It's the outbreak of
infectious disease.
The entire world is experiencing
the same outbreak.
[Takashi] So what? It's some
kind of epidemic?
This is exactly like the
Spanish flu in 1918.
[Saya] More than 600 million
people got infected...
and 50 million people died
from it.
Remember how much a panic Swine
flu caused? Well square that.
Not to be disagreeable,
but I think this is more
like the Black Death from
the 14th century.
One third of the European
population died.
You're smarter than you look.
So how did the outbreak
finally ended?
Well there are many theories.
It usually stops when too many
humans die.
There wouldn't be enough people
to spread the disease.
[Kota] But now...
All the dead people still move
and start attacking you.
Are you saying that there's
no reason for this outbreak
to stop?
The weather's going to be hot.
They might not be able to move
if their flesh decomposes...
and they become skeletons.
[Saeko] How long does it take
for that to happen?
In summers, some parts of the
body could become skeletal
in about twenty days.
But it takes considerably
longer during winter.
A couple months. That's not too
terribly long.
[Saya] You're kidding. She's
not smarter than she looks.
So what're saying?
[Saya] Medical logic doesn't
apply to those dead corpses...
that move around and
attack humans.
Worst case scenario, they might
never decompose.
First thing we find out is if
our families are okay.
Then we need to find some place
safe to hold up for a while.
[Saeko] But no matter where we
go, we're going to need a plan.
Teams! We need to team up!
Let's try to pick up survivors
whenever we can.
Let's do it.
What's the best way outta here?
Sorry to break it to you,
stupid,
but we're gonna just have
to go out the front.
Let's go!
[Saeko] Let me make
something clear.
There's no need for you to
engage in a fight unless
it's necessary.
Do whatever you can to avoid
a fight, you got it?
Remember, they're sensitive
to sounds so keep it quiet.
And they're strong enough to
rip through regular doors.
And once they've got a hold
on you, they're gonna tear
you to shreds.
So be careful.
[scream]
Takuzo...
Aw shit...
Stay back!
[thwack]
[Naomi] Uh.. Thank you...
[Saeko] Keep it down.
Has anyone been bitten yet?
What? No, no one.
It looks okay.
We'll be all right.
We're gettin' outta here.
Do any of you want to come
with us?
[Naomi] S..Sure!
[Takashi] Man, there're a
bunch of Them.
From what I can tell, the only
thing they react to are sounds.
They can't see us, so it's
pointless to hide from Them.
[Takashi] Why don't you go down
there and prove that theory?
But even if we keep going
through inside the school,
once we get attacked we're
going to be stuck.
We have to go through the gate,
we don't have any choice.
Someone needs to go and confirm
Takagi's theory. Don't suppose
you want to volunteer?
I'll go. I'll do it.
No! You stay, I'll go.
I think I should go ahead first.
[Takashi] I think you should
just stand by, just in case.
Takashi, why?
[Takashi] I don't know.
[Rei] You don't know?
Seriously, I don't know.
[Rei] Taka‐
[Saeko] Don't!
I understand, but you can't
interfere with him.
[Saeko] This was his decision.
[groaning and wheezing]
[heartbeat]
So, they really can't see me?
If that's the case...
[thud]
[clang]
Run!
Why did you open your
big mouth?!
We could've made it here just by
taking care of the ones that are
close by...
if you hadn't said anything!
The noise would've
echoed anyway!
Just start swinging!
There're too many!
Forget talking.
Just run!
[Takashi] Run!
Takuzo!
Naomi, run!
[scream]
[Naomi] Takuzo!
[Saya] Just forget him!
Once you get bitten,
it's pointless.
[sobbing]
[Saya] Wait a minute!
You heard me, didn't you?
He's not gonna make it!
Why are you going back to him?!
[Shizuka] I understand...
If the entire world turned
into this,
I'd rather die with the person
that I love.
Oh shut up Dr. Bleeding Heart!
[Kota] Look out!
[Saya] What?!
Don't you worry, Takagi.
Oh you rude little otaku!
How dare you interrupt me
while I'm talking? Why would
you do that?!
[Kota] I don't know 'cause
I really like your voice...
Nice to see that you two
are getting along.
Miss Shizuka, the key!
Target, confirmed.
Got a clear shot, all good.
Ready... aim...
Hurry up and shoot the
damn thing!
Let's go, everybody's inside!
You go! Ladies first!
It's different from my
little bug!
Let's see, gas, brake,
and there's the clutch...
[distant] Help!
Hey! Wait!
[pleading]
Who's that?
That's Mr. Shido of Class 3‐A.
Shido...
[Shizuka] We can go now!
[Takashi] Wait just a little
bit longer!
They're in front of us.
Any more and we won't be able
to drive through here.
[Takashi] Run 'em down!
If Dr. Boobs tries to drive
over that many, we'll flip
the bus.
We don't have to save him!
Jesus, what do you mean
we don't have to save him?!
We don't have to help him!
We should just live him
here to die!
Hurry, everyone!
You're going to be all right!
Okay, Mr. Shido.
But I'm not even sure if we
can make it there at this rate.
[student] I sprained my ankle!
Help me up!
Poor boy. How tragic.
Well, I guess that's it for
you then.
[sobbing]
[Shido] The world we've known
is over.
The powerless have no place
in the new one.
[scream]
[Takashi] Okay go!
[Shizuka] Hang on!
To the gate!
[Shizuka] I know!
They're not humans anymore...
[Shizuka] They're not
people anymore!
They're not alive anymore!
[engie rev]
Can't believe we did it.
[Kota] Yeah.
Thank God we did!
I take it you have been
appointed leader?
There's no such thing.
We just work together in order
to live, that's all.
[Shido] That's not good...
In order to survive, we
definitely need a leader,
a leader who bears everything
with valor, with confidence.
You'll regret this.
I guarantee that you'll regret
that you helped him!
[Yamada] The city!
[upbeat music]
[engine starting]
[♪]
[wheezing]
[thwack]
[boy] Shit!
Like I said, it's only
dangerous if we keep going!
First of all, why do we have to
go with Komuro and the others?
[Tsunoda] You guys are the
ones who decided to go back
to the city.
Maybe we shoulda just looked for
a safe place inside the school.
If you ask me, we were better
off where we were!
[Maruyama] He's right!
I kinda agree with Tsunoda.
We should barricade
ourselves somewhere‐
[screech]
Okay you all, that's enough!
I can't focus on the driving
with all this yelling!
Yeah, whatever...
How about you tell me what
you want to do.
I just can't stand this guy!
[Tsunoda] I hate him!
Sheez...
[Takashi] Why?
What the hell did I ever do to
you? I don't even know you.
You know!
[Rei] Asshole.
[clapping]
[Shido] Bravo!
Simply outstanding teamwork.
I'm impressed.
I commend both of you.
[Shido] At any rate, a conflict
like that only proves my point.
We need a leader. We do.
Surely neither of you want such
a difficult responsibility on
your shoulders.
So, you're going to run for
the position then?
I'm a teacher, Miss Takagi.
And while mature, all of you
are barely in your teens.
That alone makes it very clear
who's more qualified to assume
such a role.
I have experience. Why just
moments ago, I saved all of
these brave students!
[Shido] What do you say, guys?
There, it's been decided. The
majority seems to have made the
choice quite clear, yes?
[Takashi] Rei!
No way! I won't do it!
I'm not staying here with him!
[Takashi] Get back in the bus...
Well, there's nothing
I can do...
if you don't want to act in
accordance with all of us.
What "us"? What are you
talking about?!
[rustle]
Komuro!
[Takashi] Wait!
Get back on the bus. When we get
to the city, we'll get off.
I don't want you to leave!
That's why I told you that
you'd regret this!
No! We'll both regret this!
[honk]
Okay, you need to punch it!
Wha‐ Huh?
[Takashi] So much for gettin'
back on the bus...
Komuro, are you all right?
[Takashi] At the police station!
Meet up at the east
police station.
What time?
[Takashi] 7 o'clock.
If not today, then tomorrow
at the same time.
Looks like we're not taking
this freeway anymore.
Okay, I'll turn around and
find another way.
[fzzt]
Okay, we gotta go!
[boom]
Dammit...
Dick...
[thud]
[Rei] Takashi...
Let's go.
[Rei] Are we going to walk
to the city?
[Takashi] If there's no
other way.
Oh, wait...
He was wearing a helmet...
[engine starting up]
Do you even have a license?
[Takashi] Getting a ticket
is the least of our problems.
What are you waiting for?
Get on.
[Takashi] All that time,
I had no idea that this
world...
was already over.