[student] Move! I'm gonna
frickin' kill you, son of
a bitch!
[panic]
People are eating people.
This isn't even funny.
Can't be...
this can't be happening...
Can it, Mommy?
It's not, right?!
Takagi, where do you think
you're running to?
And what exactly was your
brilliant plan?
I was gonna talk to the teachers
in the faculty room and then go
to th‐
[Saya] That's pointless!
What do you think a bunch of
stupid teachers can do about it?
But, Takagi...
This is just... It's kinda...
Because of this I...
[Kota] I should...
[Saya] I've got a question
for you.
[Kota] What is it?
Do you want to die or do
you want to live?
[Kota] Well, that's... Um...
[knocking]
They had the same idea as you.
[Saya] Let's see how it works
for them.
[students] Sir! Sir!
You want to live, right?!
Then stick with me!
[Saya] Let's go, chubby!
[hurried footsteps]
[Hisashi] Come on, do it for me.
I want to stay myself until
the end.
[Rei] He's not turning!
He's not turning into one
of them! Don't do it!
What's the matter?
[Takashi] I was thinking what
the hell is really going on.
[Rei] That's a
straightforward answer.
[Rei] What's the point of lying
about it?
I think I should let my dad
know that I'm all right.
Let me use your cell?
[Takashi] I understand that he's
a police officer, but we can't
even connect to 110.
[Rei] I know this secret number
that he told me not to call
unless it's an emergency.
[ringing]
It got through!
Dad?!
[Tadashi] Hello?
Takashi? Is that you?
Dad listen! Daddy we're at
school there's be‐
[Tadashi] Hello, Takashi?
You must have got this
number from Rei.
Is Rei okay?! Is she with you?!
Are you both‐
Daddy! What's the matter?
Can't you hear me?!
[Tadashi] Listen carefully.
The entire city is in
[Tadashi] panic mode right now.
[Rei] Daddy! Dad‐
[gunshot]
[Tadashi] You need to get out
of there! You understand?!
The city is already in
panic mode!
You need to evacu‐
[phone cuts out]
[Rei] No service?!
But I just called him!
I don't understand!
Rei!
Takashi...
[Rei] My dad...
He didn't know that it was me at
all. He didn't even know me!
[Kota] Takagi, I know it's
against school rules, but do
you have your cell phone on you?
[Saya] I'm a straight‐A student!
Besides, even if I had one,
who would I call?
[Kota] Well, the police maybe?
God, you're so stupid.
Look how serious this is.
There's no way people haven't
called them already,
but yet we haven't heard
a single siren.
[Saya] So, now you know.
So this is happening all over?
Gee, ya think?!
I'm sure the police have been
dealing with this already,
but look at how things are.
[Kota] I wonder if we should
call the Self‐Defense Force
or something?
[Saya] I wouldn't expect
much from them.
[Kota] I know that they can't
conduct any defense or public
security operations...
without government's
order, but...
That's not what I meant!
Well, what did you mean exactly?
They're just like the police.
What do you think would happen
if people were eating people
in all the cities out there?
[Saya] Listen:
There are 130 million people.
How many of them do you think
work for the Self‐Defense Force?
And what if the same things have
been happening inside the
Self‐Defense Force?
[Saya] Come on! We need to go!
[Kota] Ah! Okay!
[Saya] Jesus! The only reason
I have to stay with
this dumbass...
is because Komuro isn't here.
I'm such a nice person.
[Ishii] O...Okada...
Okada?!
Damn it!
[Ishii] Forgive me! Forgive me!
Forgive me! Forgive me!
Forgive me!
What should I do?
[Shizuka] I can't get hold
of the police or the
fire department.
I can treat them, but once
they're bitten, they're
bound to die.
And once they die,
they'll resurrect.
This is exactly like that George
Romeo movie I once saw.
I don't think it's the time
to be impressed!
[Ishii] Let's get out of here,
Miss Shizuka!
Hold on a second.
[Shizuka] Let me take all the
stuff I can carry.
[Ishii] Just do it quickly.
[crack]
Miss Shizuka!
Miss Shizuka,
get out of here, quick!
Hey, I'm sorry, what was your
name again, please?
What?
Oh goodness...
Huh?
I'm the captain of the
kendo club, Saeko Busujima,
a sophomore.
What's your name, kid?
I..Ishii Kazu...
[Saeko] Ishii, you did a great
job protecting Dr. Marikawa.
I commend your courage.
You do know what happens to you
once you get bitten.
Do you want your parents or
friends to see you like that?
If the answer is no,
I will end your life as
painlessly as I can,
but I've never killed
anyone before.
Pl... Please do that.
Wait, what are you gonna do?
[Saeko] You're the school
doctor, I got it.
But stay out of it.
This young man is going to die
with honor.
And I'm going to make sure that
he does.
[crash]
[Kota] Okay, we're here,
but what do we do now?
Although, I do see some things
that would come in‐
Just shut up, you chubby‐geek.
[Saya] Lock the door so
they won't come in.
[Kota] I..I locked it.
Are you going to use them
as weapons?
You're one of those
basement shut‐in's,
one of those "military nerds" or
"gun geeks", aren't you?
Come on, at least you've seen
this thing before. I mean it was
in that Mel Gibson movie.
A nail gun...
And it's gas.
[Saya] Hell yeah!
We won't be able to carry
it around...
if it was one of those
compressor types, right?
God, you're fat and stupid.
[Kota] So you like movies?
Don't be ridiculous!
I'm a genius, so I
know everything...
[bang]
[Kota] We got an extra tank,
and the nails...
We're all set.
Why are you so calm, cool
and collected?
They're coming!
[Saya] They're in the hallway!
It weighs around four kilograms.
It's as heavy as some old
assault rifle.
But I can't stabilize
my aim this way.
I need to attach a sight too it.
Hey, you, are you listening
to me?!
[Saya] Hi..Hirano?
[scream]
Hirano!
Gotcha!
Hirano?
Are you ready?
Yeah!
[Takashi] Now turn it!
Shit!
You see the drill and the nails
over there?
Will you put them in a bag
or something?
Excuse me?!
You're nobody to me.
What makes you think you can
order me around?
Pretty please with sugar on top?
All right.
Takashi!
I'm okay.
[Takashi] I didn't like most of
you fucks then...
and I sure as hell don't
like you now!
Take this!
[Saya] Hey, what are you doing?
You hold this too.
[Kota] Um, okay...
Hey, Takagi, can I‐ can I ask
you something?
What?
[Kota] Well, why are you
with me?
Why? Because I'm such a
nice person.
Yeah, I can see that. Oh well.
Hey, you're on the ball all
of a sudden.
Something click in you or what?
I think I found my calling!
[Saya] Behind you!
[Takashi] The fire hose...
Not too shabby.
I figured the water pressure
would be strong enough.
Don't you remember?
During the fire drill when we
were in junior high,
[Saya] Hisashi and you got...
[Takashi] Yeah, I remember.
[Rei] I think it should be
okay now.
How I admire your optimism.
You sure about this?
Let's go!
[footsteps]
[Rei] Where do we run to?
To my house.
Go there, get supplies we need,
and meet up with other people
who haven't turned yet.
Work together and get
some place safe.
Sounds like a plan to me.
Y..Yeah, you're right!
Now that I know that
my dad's okay...
Oh, we should probably call your
house to make sure they're all
right too.
Waste of time; Nobody's home.
My dad won't be back in town
till next week...
and my mom's a school teacher
so she won't be home until
after 5.
Besides, they get on my nerves.
Well they're parents. That kind
of comes with the job.
[Takashi] I didn't really
mean that.
The truth is I was a
little scared.
Look at this place.
And my mom... she's some place
just like this.
[Kota] Wh..What are you doing?
Just be quiet.
Do you see that? They don't even
react when something hits their
bodies, the big dumbasses.
[Saya] Their senses are dead.
They only respond to the sound.
Most likely they can't
see either.
Otherwise, they wouldn't bump
into the locker.
Well, what about heat?
I'm sure we'll get plenty of
opportunities to find out.
[Saya] Let's go.
So, we're‐ we're going outside?
You think we're hanging
around here?
I kinda... I hate walking.
And that's why you're so fat!
You need to put down the
Walmart Cheetos and exercise!
[gasp]
[Kota] What?
[Saeko] The faculty room?
Jesus, what a pain in the ass.
But all the car keys are in
that room. That's where they
keep them.
[Shizuka] Why don't you just
kill them?
You've done so well this far,
why stop now?
One or two at a time, believe
me, no problem. And I wouldn't
think twice about doing it.
But they come at you in packs.
And don't be fooled, they're a
lot stronger than they look.
Once they grab you, it's hard
to get loose.
Wow, I'm impressed.
Ow! I hate these stupid
floor mats! Jeez!
What you're wearing isn't
exactly made for running.
What?
[Shizuka] Are you crazy?!
This is Christian Dior!
Your clothes or your life?
Which one is more important?
Both are!
[crash]
What was that?
It came from the faculty room.
[Saya] If you keep shooting
them, how will we learn
about them?
[Kota] You know, you could help
me fight 'em too!
You stupid, fat idiot!
That's what I have you for!
[Kota] The magazine is
almost empty!
You think that's my problem?
Hurry up and just reload it!
But they're‐ they're right
behind you...
[Saya] Huh?
[Kota] See?
[scream]
Hi..Hirano!
[click]
Oh no! I'm out!
Get away... Get away!
Takagi!
[Saya] Get back!
Stay back!
Get away!
[whir]
I can't take it anymore!
Someone please!
[Saeko] I'll take the
right side.
[Takashi] Rei!
[Rei] I'll hold the left.
Oh?
[sobbing]
Takagi...
Takagi, are you okay?
[Saya] Miyamoto...
[Saeko] You already know
the school doctor,
Marikawa, right?
And I'm Saeko Busujima from
Class 3‐A.
I'm Takashi Komuro from
Class 2‐B.
Miss Busujima, I remember you
won the national championship
last year.
I'm Rei Miyamoto. I'm in the
spear martial arts club.
Oh and I'm Kota Hirano from
Class B, just F.Y.I.
Nice to meet you.
[Saya] Why are you guys
being all warm and fuzzy?
Why are you being so polite
to her, Miyamoto?
You flunked last year,
you're the same age,
she's not your elder.
[Kota] What are you talking
about, Takagi?
Don't talk to me like
I'm stupid!
I'm a smarter than all of
you combined!
You should be lucky I'm even in
the same school as you!
I'm a... I'm a...
[Saeko] It's okay,
that's enough.
Look at me. All of these
blood stains...
Now mom will have to take
it to the cleaners.
[wailing]
[Takashi] What do you think?
[Kota] Yeah.
I think that's enough right now.
Let's take a quick break.
Hey, just wondering...
Are you okay?
Huh?
You... wear glasses?
Shut up! My contact
lenses keep on moving around.
She wears glasses...
Here you go...
Oh, thanks.
Dr. Marikawa, where's the
car key?
Oh, it's in my purse somewhere.
Are you sure your car is big
enough to fit all of us?
[Shizuka] Well, now that I
think about it...
What about the microbus we
use for the clubs' away games?
Looks like the keys are
on the wall hook.
Hey guys, I see the bus.
[Shizuka] That's fine, but where
are we going?
We're going to make sure that
our families are okay.
We'll start with the family who
lives closest from here.
If you're worried about your
family, we'll bring them
with us.
[Takashi] After that, we'll look
for a safe place and...
What's wrong?
[Rei] What is this?
[Takashi] What's wrong, Rei?
[reporter] The government
has begun to consider the
emergency measures...
against the outbreaks that have
been occurring in locations
around the city.
However, all the
political parties‐
Outbreaks? What do they
mean "outbreaks"?
It's been feared that more than
10,000 have been victimized
in Saitama area so far.
The governor has already
called for the‐
[gunshot]
Already declared the state
of emergency...
and requested the emergency
disaster relief...
It's a gunshot. It looks like
the police are finally using
firearms!
From what I can see, they're...
No... No!
[scream]