[copilot] I finished checking
on the passengers.
We don't have anyone who's
injured or has a high fever.
[copilot] Or who's already dead.
Your family, they're all in
Tokyo, aren't they?
No one's answered any
of my calls.
[copilot] Tokonosu Tower,
JX089 ready to take off.
JX089, Tokonosu Tower, uh you
might want to keep us on
runway status.
We have a little bit of a...
problem.
[Rika] What a scumbag.
He's an actor.
He came from Tokonosu for
shooting the film.
Distance 4500.
[Tajima] Angle of elevation
minus six,
almost no wind, no need for
correction.
All right, looks like you've
got a green light.
[bang]
[gun fire]
[Tajima] Bravo!
Confirming all targets on the
runway are now neutralized.
Over.
[sigh]
What are you doing?
I've been laying on my
boobs all morning.
They feel almost numb.
You know I can massage
'em for you.
I'd let you if you were a
better sniper than me.
Oh come on! You're one of
the top five shooters in
the force!
What do I rank? Fifteen?
Guess you're not feeling
them then.
[Tajima] So how do you think
they got here?
I mean this is an airport on an
island. You can only get here
by boat.
They've been restricting
the entry, right?
[Rika] Only important officials,
and technicians they need
to maintain the airport,
and their family members.
Someone among them must have
gotten infected.
It's not that bad right now,
but we don't know how long it
stays that way.
[Tajima] Who knows what
would've happened if they
wouldn't have had us come along?
These guys would've been fucked.
Although, it's not like we have
an endless supply of bullets
or anything.
So, you're going to run away?
[Tajima] No, I'm not.
At least, not yet.
[Rika] I'm going to the city.
Sooner or later.
[Tajima] You got a boyfriend
or something?
[Rika] I've got a friend there.
[traffic]
[Shido] Exactly, that's why
we should secure a safe
place first,
then make moves together
rather than making random
moves on our own.
Isn't that why you voted
a leader?
[Shido] Truly we should wait
until we're ready to act as
a disciplined group...
to confirm the safety of our
family members.
Going off half cocked on
our own...
[Saya] Hirano! Stop.
[Shido] will only lead
to inevitable tragedy.
Takagi... Morning.
Is it time to get up already?
Yes, it's morning.
Ugh and you're drooling.
Sorry...
[Kota] Look at that.
I think it's better to evacuate
to the suburbs.
Cars are not the only way
to get outta here.
[Kota] The airport on
the ocean! You're right!
It's far too dangerous to be
anywhere in the city.
I bet a bunch of people are
trying to escape to some island,
or some isolated area with some
kind of strong military presence
or something.
Like, Okinawa?
But the American military
that's stationed there isn't
there to fight...
Oh! But there's
Self‐Defense Forces.
If the military has taken
appropriate measures,
then I'm betting Hokkaido or
Kyushu should be okay too.
If planes are leaving, then all
the flights are heading to
those areas.
So you think maybe we should
head that way too?
[Saya] It's too late!
The areas with a heavy presence
of Self‐Defense Forces...
and American military may
be managing to keep Them
under control,
but I'm sure they've already
started to adopt a stern policy
toward letting anybody else in.
No, sooner or later, it's going
to be that way everywhere in
the world.
I mean what would you do in the
same situation?
[Kota] I'd seclude myself.
What would happen if everyone
in this world starts thinking
that way?
What if they start focusing
only on keeping their community
as small as possible in order
to survive?
You really ask some very
relevant questions, you
know that?
What are you talking about?
Look at him.
[Saya] You can already see
that in him.
Although, I doubt that he
knows it himself.
You know, this all
happened overnight.
Should I interrupt them?
Forget the pervy teacher and
slutty little Sally over there.
I should consult with someone
that I can trust.
Jeez, I could have talked
to Komuro if he were here!
Yeah, you like Komuro. I know.
Don't be ridiculous!
[sigh]
[Saya] What?!
I'm getting worried about Komuro
and the others.
[Saeko] I hope they can hold
on till we meet up.
[boom]
[screaming]
[gunshot]
[laughing]
That's right, you run!
All of you, run like Hell!
[gunfire]
[Rei] This is absolutely nuts.
It's like a war.
And we're front row, center
for it.
Dangerous place to be.
[engine revving]
Hold on tight.
Hey!
Hold on to me, Rei!
[gunshot]
We're not dead! Why are these
maniacs shooting at us?!
The whole world's going
crazy, Rei.
We can't trust anyone.
We can't trust anyone...
What? The bridge is
straight ahead!
I know, but did you see it?
[Takashi] At this rate,
we don't know when we'll
be able to cross.
We'll head to Onbetsu Bridge
and meet up with the teachers
and the others.
[screaming]
[police] I repeat! We want
everyone to follow the police
officers' directions...
and proceed calmly!
The entire city is under
traffic restriction.
Anyone who tries to cross the
river without permission will
be stopped.
Crossing the river by foot
is not permitted.
[rattle]
Come back here!
Did you just look up her dress?
Move, bitch!
So annoying, you old hag!
Get outta the way!
[police] You, over there!
Get back now!
Do not try to cross the bridge!
This is the last warning!
Give me a break!
Who's gonna listen to a bunch
of stupid cops?
It's every man for himself
these days, asshole!
You're so cool, Hide‐chan!
[police] Use the water!
I‐ w‐what?
There must be some mistake!
I was just going along to
be safe!
[police] Blast them!
[Shido] I know we're
no longer in school,
but I hope that you would
all continue to live with
the pride...
your school has instilled in
each and every one of you!
[Shido] Pride of unity! It is
that pride that will keep
us together!
Not vainglorious pride in
ourselves, but pride as a
group, a family!
And realize this, my dear
friends! Komuro and Miyamoto...
were unfit to be in our family!
This guy's a God damn maniac.
[Saeko] You got that right.
[Shido] We must stand together
in order to survive!
Sounds like he's a recruiter
for some kind of cult
religious group.
He doesn't just sound
like it; it is.
[Saya] And look at the
slobbering idiots hinging
on his every word.
Like a bunch of
Scientologists...
Or rather, Shido‐tologists.
I need to get out of here.
Given the condition
on the road,
Looks like we're going to have
to give up our ride.
We have to somehow get across
Onbetsu Bridge and head to the
east police station.
We're still supposed to meet
up with Komuro.
You're sure quite concerned
about Komuro, aren't you?
Aren't you worried about your
own family?
Course I am, but my father is my
only family, and he's at the
dojo overseas.
So the only people I really need
to be worrying about right now,
is myself and Komuro. I really
don't care about anybody else.
And just look at me. I mean,
seriously, if any of us are
going to make it out of here
alive...
it's going to be me, right?
[nervous laughter]
So, where is everyone's house?
The other side of the
bridge; the same area
with Komuro's.
[Kota] Oh, my parents are not
in the neighborhood,
but I‐I'd go anywhere as long
as I'm with Takagi.
Eeew!
So tell me, Hirano,
where's your family?
They close?
My father is a jewelry merchant,
so he's gone to Amsterdam
to buy stones.
My mother is a fashion designer,
so she's been staying
in Paris, to‐
Christ! Do you expect us to
believe all that crap?!
And if it were a manga,
Daddy would be the captain
of a cruise ship, a giant
luxury liner!
My grandpa actually was.
And my grandmother was a
concert violinist.
[Saya] Ugh, why couldn't he be
better looking?
[Shizuka] So, what are we
going to do?
I want to come along with
all of you.
[Saya] Are you sure?
Both of my parents passed
away years ago,
and my relatives live far away.
I know I shouldn't be
saying this,
but I... I think Mr. Shido
is kind of a douchebag.
So, what do we do?
I'm not very familiar with
this area.
We really need to check on
Onbetsu Bridge first.
Um, what's the matter, everyone?
[Shido] We need to work
together, otherwise none
of us are ever‐
Thanks for the offer, but I'm
gonna pass, Mr. Shido.
We've got our own plans.
And FYI, this is no field trip.
[Saya] I have no obligation
to be with you. I never had
any classes with you anyway.
I see...
If that's what you've decided,
go right ahead. I won't stop
you, Takagi.
How could I? This is a free
country, not some sort of
iron‐fisted dictatorship.
However...
I'm afraid you will have
to remain, Miss Marikawa.
[Shido] Losing the doctor
is a major blow to our
current situation.
Would you please stay?
What do you say?
[Shido] There are students
who are relying on you.
[bang]
Y‐You shot at me!
[Kota] I missed you on purpose.
You douchebag.
But y‐you're not a violent
student like that...
How many of my fellow students
do you think I killed in
school yesterday?
And I could kill you too
for all the ways you always
made fun of me!
[Kota] I was holding back...
I was holding back for a
long time!
I was holding it back because
I just wanted to have a
normal life!
But there's no need to do
that anymore!
Nothing we know is
normal anymore!
That's why I'm able to kill now.
I can even kill living
people too.
Maybe start by the ones who
made fun of me!
I made fun? You misunderstood!
I've always held you in such
high esteem!
If you want to go,
now's the time to do it.
I'll make sure he doesn't
stop you!
You're such a man,
I'm impressed.
Mr. Shido?
[Rei] It's the same here.
What should we do?
Should we try a different
bridge or something?
I'm sure they're all the same.
Probably every bridge
is blocked.
[Takashi] What's the point of
policing unless they block Them?
Damnit.
We need to cross the bridge and
get to the east police station
by 7:00.
[Rei] How? That's a little
easier said than done.
[Takashi] Give me a sec,
I'm thinking!
I wish there were...
Well there isn't!
So there's no use
bringing it up.
[bang]
Gunshot?!
No, it... that was a...
Um, hey, maybe we were better
off staying on the bus with
Mr. Shido.
[Shizuka] Just throwing that
out there.
Hold on, weren't you the one
who said that you thought he
was a douchebag?
As a matter of fact, I did,
but he wouldn't be the first
douchebag I was stuck on a
bus with.
Just to let you know,
I'm running out of the nails!
Do you want to borrow this?
I really don't do
hand‐to‐hand combat.
I can't say the same...
I'm actually quite fond of it!
Wait a minute!
[Rei] Are you nuts?!
[Shizuka] No!
Takagi!
Oh no!
[in unison] Holy shit!
Hirano!
Double‐tap, baby!
Give me your hand!
[Shizuka] Amazing...
[Saeko] Looks like it's all
cleared for now.
They sure were tough to beat.
Tough for everybody but
you maybe.
[Rei] Miss Shizuka!
[Shizuka] Oh, Miyamoto,
what a coincident!
[muffled]
That's, "what a coincidence".
You too, Komuro!
[Saeko] This must mean that
Tokonosu Bridge is also blocked.
Right, there's no way out.
I have to confess,
I'm really glad that you're
okay, Komuro.
[Takashi]
Glad you're all right too.
What about me?
I'm glad you're okay too,
all of you.
What are you doing?
Komuro, what is this?!
How did you get it?
Where are the extra bullets?
[Kota] This is Smith & Wesson's
M37 Airweight,
that the police use, right?
[Takashi] I'll tell you about
it later.
[Kota] Oh man! Feel the weight!
How good it feels!
[Saeko] We got off the bus
because the road was blocked,
but we haven't been able to
cross the river.
[Saya] The water has risen,
so going further upstream
won't help, I guess.
[Rei] Then, what should we do?
I have a thought.
It's been such a stressful day,
why don't we just
call it quits for now?
[Kota] C‐Call it a day?
Why yes. My friend's flat is
nearby. It's just a short walk
from here.
[Saya] Your boyfriend's place?
Oh no, no, no, no!
It's nothing like that!
It's just my girl
friend's apartment.
She's always busy working
and traveling with her job.
She gave me the key so I could
go there and look after the
place when she's away.
Have a nice day!
Is it a high‐rise?
Does it have a good view
of the surroundings?
Oh, yeah!
It's a duplex,
standing along the river.
There's a convenience store
nearby too.
Oh, and a car! You know, that
one that looks like a tank.
The thing that drinks gas?
Big! The really big one!
I don't care about a car
as much as a shower.
I don't think I've ever felt
dirtier in my life.
I couldn't agree with you more.
[thud]
What do you mean by that?!
[Takashi]
I'll go check on it with her.
Come on, let's go.
[Shizuka] Oh, okay.
[Shizuka] Oh! It's been so
long since I've felt
something like this!
Um, you're talking about the
motorcycle aren't you?
What? What did you say?
I can't hear you!
[Takashi] I‐I was just saying...
[Shizuka] I can't hear you!
[Takashi] I just said...
[Takashi] I said‐!
[Kota] A Hum‐Vee! It's the
military model too!
Told you.
It looks like a tank, right?
Exactly what kind
of friend is she?
I bet They can't jump over
the fence,
so we should be able to have a
good night's sleep.
Let's hurry up and‐
[groan]
Komuro, will this work?
Yeah, good enough.
Stay back.
Don't take chances and be
sure to cover for each other.
[Takashi] Let's go!
Looking back on it,
it seemed like that's when
we all changed.
We weren't just running
away anymore.
We were attacking first
to survive.
We didn't question it.
It just became instinct.
And it became the only thing
we knew.
It didn't take that long...