[radio] We've got information
on the target!
Moments before the
Trident warhead was launched,
they confirmed four Delta
Foxtrot 21 from the Tsuka Base!
After that, the target is
Alpha, Bravo, Charlie, Delta.
Repeat:
[captain] Soon, we may be
the only ones left.
Ready, sir.
Shift the system to BMD mode.
[captain] CIC designated target,
begin shooting.
Commence firing!
[in unison] Fire!
[crewman]
Ten seconds until intercept.
9... 8... 7...
6... 5... 4...
Standby!
[gasp]
[crewman] Our SM‐3 shot down
the target Alpha!
Kirishima and the USS Shiloh
shot down Bravo and Charlie
as well!
There's one more missile left.
That's dedicated for the target
for Curtis Wilbur.
[captain]
Shit! What the hell's going on?
[radio]
Curtis Wilbur, this is Kongo!
Why aren't you shooting?
Come in! Come in!
[wheezing]
[astronaut] One missile left.
Where's it headed?
Wait a minute,
could it be the States?
Doesn't look like it... Hold on.
[man] Hey, what the hell
just happened?
That light!
Did anybody see the light?!
You're the police, aren't you?
What was it?!
[Rika] It's simple.
Starting today, all of our
nights are going to be
darkness itself.
Yes! Yes, I did it!
Now I remember!
Oh, yes! I'm sure of it!
There's no doubt!
[Arisu]
What's the matter with her?
I just remembered!
I remembered my friend's
phone number!
You mean the one with all
the guns and the Hum‐Vee?
[Shizuka] That's right!
She's in the SAT,
the Special Assault Team,
so she must be still alive!
[Shizuka] More importantly,
oh, give me the phone!
Uh, okay...
Now, let's see... There's the
one, and there's the two,
and the three and the four,
yeah, all the numbers are
where they're supposed‐
Do you want me
to press it for you?
You're going to make me mess
up, so don't interrupt me. 'Kay?
[ringing]
[Rika] Hello?
Rika?! Oh thank God,
you're alive!
[Arisu] I'm happy for you!
I was so worried about you.
Takashi...
Well,
now it looks like we can...
[Shizuka] Oh, a lot of things
have happened to me too, but...
Cut to the chase, will you?
Where are you right now?
My place?
[Shizuka]
That place isn't good anymore.
Oh, we borrowed
your guns and stuff.
[Rika] That's okay. Just tell me
where you are right now‐
[bzzt]
[Shizuka] Uh, hello? Rika?!
Jesus Christ, what happened?
That light...
Oh, no way...
[Saya]
Miyamoto, check the gun's sight!
What? But why?
[Saya] Just check it!
Yours should be using the IC!
How is it? Do you see the dot?
Well, I can't see.
I knew it.
[Takashi]
Takagi, what's going on?
Hey, what are you doing?
Hurry up!
[guard] Something's wrong
with the engine.
What happened?
The PC went dead
when we lost the power.
Someone, please help me!
I think my husband's having
a heartattack! Help me!
What's wrong with these
God damn breaks?
Where's the emergency break?!
Mr. Shido, in front of you!
[crash]
I‐I‐I'm alive...
H‐Hey...
[guard] We're in trouble...
Cell phone's no good.
All right, let's get ready
for 'em!
No way, man! I'm leaving!
Come back here!
Fuckin' pussy!
Shit!
[gunshots]
[Takashi] HANE?
[Saya] High‐altitude
nuclear explosion. Duh.
Do I have to explain
everything to you people?
[Saya] The explosion of the
nuclear warhead in the upper
atmosphere creates Compton
electrons.
Gamma rays then sputter those
electrons from the
atmospheric molecules.
The sputtered electrons
accelerate and spiral along the
Earth's magnetic field,
generating an electromagnetic
pulse and such effect is lethal
for electronic devices.
That pulse can travel
through anything that
works as an antenna,
and fries its
integrated circuit.
[Saeko] So, basically,
right now we can't‐
[Saya] Connect the dots, hunny.
All electronics are dead.
What? So that means we can't use
cell phones and stuff anymore?
[Saya] Not only cell phones,
but we won't be able to
use computers.
[Saya] Cars with computers
won't work.
[Arisu] There, there. It's okay.
[Saya] The power plants will
be dead too,
unless they were implementing
EMP measures.
But I know only a small portion
of Self Defense Forces and
the government agencies are
using such measures.
Is there a way to fix it?
Daddy!
[Saya] Some cars could work if
we replace the fried parts.
And we might be able to
find undamaged cars,
which have sustained less
effect of electromagnetic waves.
They should work if they don't
have the computer chips in them.
[Soichiro] Go check right away.
[yesman] Yes, sir.
[Soichiro] Saya!
[Saya] Y‐Yes, sir?
I must say I'm impressed how
you stayed calm and rational
in this commotion.
You deserve my praise.
Daddy?
[gunshot]
[guard] Look!
Look at the barricade!
Get back! Get back!
[screaming]
Close the gate! Hurry up!
Don't let the dead come inside!
Commander, we still have
a lot of our men on the
outside of the complex!
[Soichiro] We'll lose everything
if we don't close the gate now!
Do it!
[guard] One got in!
Inside the pocket...
That's one for the home team.
I'm sorry, kid,
I was wrong about you!
Commander! Madam!
I brought this as you requested!
[in unison] What?!
Mama...
[Yuriko] Use it, Saya.
That's‐ That's a Luger P08
Holland colonial model!
I don't even know
how to use this thing!
Wait a minute! What are you
even doing with a gun?!
[Kota] The stock and
the drum magazine too?
[Yuriko] When I was working on
Wall Street, I was taking the
executive self‐defense course.
Actually, I might be a better
shooter than your father.
You will show her how to use it,
won't you, Hirano?
Yes, Mama!
No, that's not what I mean,
I meant "yes ma'am"...
Yes, Mama!
We're screwed man!
Can't hold 'em!
[creak]
Th‐They'll get in!
[wheezing]
Master, run!
Get out of here!
[screaming]
Everybody get back!
Help me!
Someone help me!
Stop it!
Just calm down and we can talk!
If you get treated
at the hospital,
I'm sure
your disease will be...
[lady] It's your fault!
I was...
I was trying very hard
to help you!
Die!
Die! Die!
[gunshot]
Shoulder the gun and
lean into it...
[Takashi]
Aim around the chest...
Fire!
Kota, here!
This shit never ends.
[Saeko] I know.
It only gets worse
as time goes on.
[Kota] We'll run out of
bullets soon too!
[Yoshioka] Commander, our scouts
have confirmed.
The troops stationed at the
house next door haven't
been attacked yet.
And I believe we can reinforce
the all the doors and gates.
[Soichiro] We'll rip through the
enemies and head to next door.
Come if you're a man and
ready to battle.
And as for the women
and children,
stay close behind immediately,
if you want to survive.
[Yuriko] Saya...
[Saya] Dad, why don't we just
barricade ourselves in the‐
They broke through
the iron gate!
What's the point of trying
to protect the house?
[Soichiro] Even if we barricade
ourselves in the mansion,
they'll still break in
and kill us all.
I thought you were going to
help your parents, were you not?
[Soichiro]
Then, you should be on your way.
Yes, sir.
[Soichiro] Hirano...
Take care of my daughter.
Dad, what do you mean by that?!
Mom?
Stop acting like a child.
Your father and I have
work to do. Deal with it.
[Yuriko] I've left you many
times during your life
and I'm sorry for that.
I hope some day you'll
forgive me.
But this time I'm leaving you
because I have to.
I'm not leaving you
because I want to.
[Saya] Mommy...
Mrs. Takagi...
Be a good girl.
But more importantly,
be a strong one.
[Yuriko] You listen to your big
brothers and big sisters, okay?
[Arisu] Okay.
[Yuriko] Now...
Get out of here!
Daddy... Mommy...
I love you so much!
Throw the dynamite!
Yes, sir!
[Saya] Mr. Maddo!
They're not here?
Lady Saya...
What are you doing down there?
You're lucky, Lady Saya.
This here's
anti‐electromagnetic pulse.
[Maddo]
It's triple copper plated.
The owner of this
must be hardcore.
So you're saying that
this car can still drive?
[Maddo] But it needs some repair
because it's been damaged.
It'll take a while.
Well then,
looks like this is
where we make a stand.
Here they come!
Doesn't look very good.
Not for us anyway, darling.
[Soichiro] Yuriko...
You are a good woman.
[Soichiro] Let's go!
Get back!
I got it!
That's so cool!
You're such a ditz!
Well that is my character
after all.
[Saya] Just get in the car!
Okay!
[gunshot]
[Kota] Just like the Alamo!
[Takashi]
That's not very encouraging.
[Kota] Tell me about it!
[Takashi] Rei!
Are you okay?
[Takashi] Let's go!
Yeah! You're right!
I wish I could have messed with
it a little more, but...
All right!
[Maddo] You're good!
Come on!
It's working!
Everyone, get back here!
Mr. Matsudo, get in the car.
I'm afraid
I can't go with ya.
My true love is here
and I'm not leaving her.
Lady Saya, please take care!
[Shizuka] Here we go!
All right!
Come here, you fuckers!
[screech]
[Rei] Which way do we go now?
[Saeko] You're looking at it.
What? It's too narrow.
[Saeko] Keep going!
Saeko!
[Soichiro] They're gone.
[Yuriko] I don't know
if we were the best parents.
But hopefully
she's learned from us.
She'll be all right.
Well now...
Then there's nothing
to hold me back!
It's okay for now, I guess.
[Saya] Please don't say
anything! Just don't!
[Kota] Takagi!
What is it?
Be sure to keep an eye out!
Hirano, what are you‐
It's okay...
[Saya] It's okay.
Hirano is...
Kota is right!
[bang]
And I hate to bring it up,
but the engine sounds strange.
Yeah, I kinda think there's
something wrong with the car.
Can I stop driving soon?
No, keep driving.
I'm sorry,
but Rei and I can't stop
until we both find our parents.
After that, we'll look for
your friend too, okay?
[Shizuka] O‐Okay!
There's a highway. Take it.
[wheezing]
There's so many...
Ahem...
Oh, well.
[Takashi]
Let's end this little road trip.
With a fuckin' bang!
[Takashi]
You're always wondering how
things are going to end.
And you make up these scenarios
in your head.
But you know what?
Every single one of them
you thought of,
you were dead wrong.
Because life, even among the
dead, keeps going.