[jet engine]
[shutter click]
[engine]
[Takashi] I stayed up late
on the night...
before the day everything
came to an end.
[Saya] That's so stupid.
[Takashi] What do you want?
Every time you have to face
something you don't like,
you come to this
stupid staircase.
It's like your own little
pity corner.
[Takashi] That's right...
Everything was normal
up until then.
I was in the sun enjoying
the luxury of feeling sorry
for myself.
If there was a ranking of the
most pathetic high schoolers
in the world,
I'd rank fourth.
But at that time everything
was already coming to an end.
And none of us ever
saw it coming.
Hey now, Mr. Tejima!
[Hayashi] Excessive
violence is...
[scream]
[panic]
[Takashi] Now that I think
about it,
I should have just forced my
way out to the outside,
no matter what.
But we didn't have time to
think, so we went to the roof.
Seemed like a good idea
at the time.
[Taksahi] Re‐
[Hisashi] Rei!
[Rei] Why?
Why is this happening?
[Takashi] There has to be
a reason.
Maybe if we can figure out
what's causing it, we can
stop it.
Or at least protect ourselves.
[vomiting]
[Takashi] Whatever Hisashi says
is always right.
I wanted to believe that too.
But I already knew
intuitively...
that the world that we'd
been familiar with was
already broken.
So, I...
Gotcha!
Take this!
[Takashi] That's right...
At that moment,
pretending that things
were normal sounded way
too dangerous.
Everything was different.
Walking down the school
hallway, weapons in
our hands...
it wasn't just a school
hallway anymore.
I used to think that high
school was Hell.
And now it was.
I wonder if anyone will come
to rescue us?
They're not coming.
Why not?
How can you be so sure?
Just like the helicopters
we saw on the rooftop of
the school.
[Takashi] They can't afford
to be rescuing us,
and maybe they'll never be
able to.
[Rei] Never?
Then what are we supposed to
do with no kind of help?!
We'll do whatever we can.
That's about it.
God, you are so predictable.
The glass isn't half empty,
with you there is no glass.
You've been this way
since kindergarten.
I only told you the truth!
[Rei] Yeah well you don't have
to be such a bummer about doing
it, you know!
[wheezing]
Let's go.
You're right...
But no matter where we go,
we're going to need a plan.
[Saeko] Teams! We need to
team up!
Let's go.
[Takashi] Making moves then
meant that we were getting
ready to face the real crisis.
We ran through the school
filled with yelling voices,
screams, life and death all
mixed together.
And then we were outside and
it was more of the same.
Just more of it.
[Shizuka] They're not
people anymore...
They're not humans anymore!
They're not alive anymore!
[engine rev]
[police] It's dangerous to
go outside!
Do not go outside your car,
no matter what!
I repeat:
Do not go outside your vehicle,
no matter what!
We move any slower,
we'll be going in reverse.
At this rate, I'm not sure if
we can cross the bridge
before dawn.
[stomach growl]
Shut up! Be quiet!
You're so disgusting!
I can't help it.
I've been so hungry...
Ever since I started PX90.
[gunshots]
It's okay.
[Shido] It's safe in here.
Mr. Shido...
You have nothing to worry
about, my darlings.
There, there. It's all right.
[clapping]
There, it's been decided. The
majority seems to have made
the choice quite clear, yes?
[Takashi] Rei!
No way! Uh‐uh!
I am not staying here with him!
[Takashi] Wait!
Get back on the bus.
I don't want you to leave!
That's why I told you
you'd regret this!
No! We'll both regret this!
[honk]
Okay, you need to punch it!
[Takashi] Basically, I wasn't
aware that the world I knew,
it was just a memory now.
Komuro, are you all right?
[Takashi] The police station!
Meet at the east
police station.
What time?
[Takashi] 7 o'clock!
If not today, then tomorrow
at the same time!
[♪]
[Rei] There's no one here.
[Takashi] Did they get away
or did they die?
[Rei] But if they die they'll
become Them.
[Takashi] Maybe they went to
find others, the ones that
are still alive.
Takashi, look at that!
No license, no helmet,
stolen bike.
I'm just asking to be
arrested, aren't I?
Oh what? After fighting that
many of Them,
don't tell me you're still
afraid of the police?
You've got a point!
[Takashi] You've got to be
kidding me...
Rei!
Wait, there's leaking gas
from that car. Don't do it.
[Rei] There could be something
in there that we could use.
What's wrong with you?
This is Armageddon! Man up!
[Rei] Do you know how to use it?
[Takashi] I've watched enough
TV. How hard could it be?
And what do they say? Don't aim
it unless you plan to shoot.
[Rei] What's the matter?
It's just a lot heavier than
I thought it'd be.
[Rei] Of course it is;
it's the real thing.
[Takashi] It can only shoot
five times?
[Rei] Takashi, here.
The grip on the other gun was
broken, but I think that the
bullets are still good.
They're bloody but
still usable.
[Takashi] Heh, I'm impressed.
My dad collects guns so I've
been around them my whole life.
Besides do you think I'd freak
out over a little blood now?
Should we get rid of these?
No, let's keep them until we can
get some target practice.
Good point and don't you feel
better now with something that
has a little more oomph?
[Rei] I wonder if they
still got gas?
[Takashi] They say any
gas station...
has a tank thats big enough to
hold enough gasoline to fill up
a thousand cars,
so they should have some.
What's the matter?
[Takashi] This gas station
is self‐service.
We can't get gas unless we
put money or a card in there.
[Rei] Then, put it in there!
With the money I have, the only
thing we're gonna get out of
this pump is fumes.
You're the worst...
I'm sorry, okay?!
I guess Hisashi would have
the cash!
Where did that come from?!
When did I ever compare you
to Hisashi?
You said I'm the worst,
didn't you?!
That means someone is the
best, right?
You must have meant Hisashi!
I didn't then, but I do now.
What do you want?
Money! I need to borrow some!
I kinda... I kinda left my
wallet in the bag.
[Takashi] Aw Jesus.
And you're riding my ass?
Just wait here.
Scream if something happens.
[♪]
Hello? Is there anybody here?
[Takashi] Nah, not working.
Oh well, I've always wanted
to do this anyway.
[crash]
What is he...?
[jingle]
He's having a field day, huh?
Come on Rei, stop giving the guy
such a hard time.
[heavy breathing]
[scream]
Oh no!
Hey, quit squirmin'!
Rei, what's wrong?
[laughing]
Hey, you've got a fuckin'
hot piece of ass here,
you know that?
You let her go!
Ha ha! Why would I do that?
You think I'd go for one of
those stanky‐ass zombie bitches?
[ruffian]
Think again motherfucker!
Jesus man, are you crazy?
That it?
[ruffian] Crazy?
Hell yeah, I am!
My family became Them right
in front of my own eyes!
I had to...
I had to smash everyone's head!
My father! My mother!
My grandma and brother!
Even my little sister too!
How can I be normal? You think I
wouldn't be fucked up
after that?!
Takashi!
Rei!
I sure like the way you scream.
[ruffian] And the way you feel.
Quite a handful there.
You're fuckin' her, aren't ya?
I bet you stickin' it to this
hot little bitch day and night.
Wait a minute...
Holy shit! You haven't!
[ruffian] You haven't got
on this yet! What a fuckin'
pussy, man!
Takashi!
[ruffian] Hey, drop the bat.
If you don't, I'll kill
this slut.
And the bike, gimmie your
fuckin' bike, man!
There's no gas in it.
[ruffian] I heard you in
the store!
Put the cash you got in the slot
and pump the motherfuckin' gas!
[clang]
[groan]
[automated voice] Please touch
the antistatic sheet before you
start pumping the gas.
[Takashi] Hey, will you let
us go now?
You can have the bike. We need
to see if our families are
all right.
[ruffian] Shut the fuck up!
I don't give a shit about
your parents!
They're gonna end up just like
my family did ya fuckin' retard.
[Takashi] It's done.
Away from the bike and
start walkin'!
[Takashi] Come on man‐
Don't take one more
fuckin' step!
Dude, I'm begging‐
Shut up or I'll fuckin'
kill you, motherfucker!
[Takashi] I've never shot
a gun before,
but somehow I don't think
I'd miss at this range.
The gas... the gasoline'd blow
us all up.
It's better than someone
stealing my girl.
[bang]
[ruffian] Asshole!
Bleeding, I'm bleeding!
Be glad I don't shoot you!
You asshole!
[Takashi] Stop it, Rei.
[Rei] But he...
We don't have time to be
screwing around with this guy.
Besides, company's coming.
[wheezing]
[engine starting]
Hey, where're you going?
You can't leave me here!
[ruffian] What kind of
fuckers are you?!
No!
Come back! Come back!
[wheezing]
[scream]
[Rei] What's the matter,
Takashi?
Why are you so quiet?
I was just thinking, stuff like
that is gonna happen over and
over again from now on.
You think so?
I mean, I guess so.
Don't worry about it.
It's over now.
[Takashi] There's no way
it's just nothing.
It's only been one day since
the beginning of the end,
but I've already killed
a person.
There's no way it's
just nothing.
[jet engine]
[shutter click]