T‐Takashi...
Rei...
Ready or not, here I come!
Don't let her escape, Komuro.
Uh, okay.
It's gonna hurt!
A little.
[Rei] No!
[Shizuka]
It's for your own good.
[Takashi] One day had passed
since Saeko and I made it to
Takagi's house.
And I have to say, that this
was the first "ordinary time"
I've had...
since this whole awful
ordeal began.
And it was kind of hot!
[Shizuka] Did it burn?
That was my special formula!
You traitor!
[Takashi] Wh‐Why?
I only held you down while
she rubbed your back.
[Rei] That's not what I meant!
Then, what was it?
[Rei] Can't you guess?
Guess? Guess what?
Guess not.
All I need is just a little bit
of medicine on me.
You don't need to call in the
school nurse.
Huh?
Get out of here.
[Takashi]
What is it all of a sudden?
[Rei] My boobs are killing me
because you used them to
balance an AK‐47!
Now get out!
Whatever, she loved it.
[thud]
[man] You idiot,
you're walking too fast!
Let me help you.
No kid, it's all right.
[idiot] You just leave this
for the big boys.
The "big boys"?
[man] Just go relax, pretty boy.
What's their problem?
[Saeko]
Don't worry about it too much.
What's the matter?
[Takashi] Oh, it's just...
It looks good on you.
Really good. Really good.
I mean...
I didn't mean it in a weird way!
It's cool, I got it!
I didn't take it that way.
[Takashi] Whew.
[laughing]
Hey, what is it?
Why are you laughing?
Did something happen?
Uh, we were just saying that
we're so glad that you're okay.
Yeah, I'm more than okay!
Looks like we all are now.
[Saya] Fine!
You're always right! Always!
Or were...
[Takashi]
What's the matter with you?
You don't have to ask
like such a prick.
[Takashi] I'm sorry.
What's the matter with you?
Maybe prick was the wrong word.
I shoulda said asshole!
I don't want to talk about it.
Just drop it. Leave me alone.
Hey, Taka‐
[Saya] I said I don't
want to talk about it!
[Takashi] What is the matter?
[Yuriko] Sorry to draw you into
our little discussion.
No, it's okay.
I guess you're used to it.
You've known each other
since kindergarten.
Yeah, some things never change.
Your house is really beautiful,
by the way.
[Takashi]
I'd always heard about it,
but I'd never thought I'd ever
see inside of it.
[Yuriko] Come to think of it,
you've never been to my
house before, have you?
[Takashi] No, never.
[Yuriko] You weren't afraid
of coming here, were you?
[Takashi]
A little intimidated, yeah...
I'm sorry.
You're honest. I like that.
[Takashi] But I heard that you
don't stay here long.
[Yuriko] No.
[Kota] This is the
carrier spring ejector.
[Saya]
You look like you're having fun.
Just wanna let you know you
should enjoy it while you can.
None of us are going to
be here forever.
[Kota] Why not, Takagi?
This house is almost
like a fortress.
Haven't you thought about
how hard it is to secure things
like electricity and water?
Things have changed lately,
you know.
[Kota] Oh, um, well...
Even under normal circumstances,
which we're not,
we'd have to
find basic necessities.
[Saya] You think we could
all just build a water
treatment plant?
Or a power station? Maybe the
zombies would help us do it.
[Yuriko] When the dead
started attacking people,
the commander sent the
Self Defense Forces to the power
plants at his own discretion.
He's not the kind of man to sit
around and wait on the prime
minister's incompetency.
If that's the case,
maybe they'll keep things
working a little longer...
[Yuriko] So optimistic.
How much longer do you think
those maintainance workers
will stay there?
They have families too,
don't they?
And their family members aren't
at the power plants.
[Takashi] So, you plan on
taking the buses and...
Correct, but only the ones
we're responsible for.
Or rather, we'll only be taking
the ones that can survive
outside of this place.
It's Darwinian, I know.
[Maddo] Hey, hey...
Hold on, that's a real gun,
isn't it?
A kid like you shouldn't
be playing with it.
[Kota] Sorry, sir.
[Saya] Mr. Maddo, is that
all you've got to say?
Oh, Lady Saya...
Um, I was just going
to let you know
that we've finished the tune‐up
on the car, the Hum‐Vee
you came here in.
[Saya]
Thank you. That'll be all.
You come from such
a prestigious family.
Wow!
[Saya] As a matter of fact,
I do. Like that matters now.
And why would you let him
talk to you like that?
Well because he's an adult.
[Saya]
You think that means anything?
We've been through
just as much as they have.
More! I'm sick of how
they're treating us.
We'd better talk to Komuro and
the others about this lack
of equity.
[Yuriko] I want her to
understand me,
but no matter what I say,
she won't listen.
Maybe you could talk to her?
She thinks that I can
convince Takagi?
I've never been able to
convince her of anything
in my whole life.
[door opening]
I don't see a reason why
everyone has to gather
around here.
[Takashi] You can barely move.
What else can we do?
I'm sorry, but what are we
talking about again?
[Saya]
Whether we can continue to move
forward as a group or not.
As a group?
It's a good point.
The group's bigger now.
We might have to think
more democratically
since there are more of us
than there were before.
It's only fair.
[Saya]
Right, we have only two options.
Whether we're going
to be absorbed or...
...separate from them.
But wait, do you really think we
have to split from the group?
[Takashi] Things are only
getting worse in the city,
and your father seems to
know what he's doing.
And your mother too.
They have a plan.
Oh don't they always?
No one knows more than I do.
Her achievements...
Don't think she won't shove them
right in your face.
[Saya]
Maybe if she would've been as
dedicated at home as she was‐
Takagi...
[Saya] God she's such a bitch!
You shouldn't talk bad
about your parents.
[Takashi] Considering the
situation we're in,
it's been really tough
for everyone.
Did I ask you to weigh in
on my family life?!
Takagis, the Takagis!
How fabulous their life must be!
[Saya] Everything had
to be just perfect.
The house and the lawn and
the parties, and most of all,
their daughter!
It was positively sufficating!
They wanted to know where I was
and what I was doing every
minute of the day!
The leash they kept me on!
That's enough‐
[Saya] No! It was never enough!
But where was that
leash yesterday?!
When I was out there,
lost in the streets,
fighting for my life!
Where the hell were they?!
Stop it, Saya!
[Saeko] Komuro!
You...
You don't know...
You have no idea...
[Saya] What I feel...
You don't know anything
about me...
[Takashi] It's not just you.
We all feel the same way.
We all feel the same way!
Don't you know
how lucky you are?
At least your parents are safe!
[Takashi] So quit whining!
[Saya] Okay...
You're right.
You can put me down now.
I'm sorry.
Yeah, you'd better be.
I forgive you.
[Saya] Now back to the subject.
Do you think we should‐
[rumble] Huh?
[Takashi] That's...
Yes.
He's the former lord
of Tokonosu.
[Saya]
The head of the Takagi family.
The man who judges
everything by his rules.
My father!
[wheezing]
[Soichiro] This man's name
is Tetsutaro Doi.
He's the former retainer of the
family who had served the
Takagi family.
He is also my best friend.
Today...
During the rescue operation,
an effort to save his
associates,
he was bitten!
[Soichiro] This is the ultimate
case of self‐sacrifice.
What he did was something noble.
Something any human being
could do.
However...
He is no longer a human.
He's become something
extremely dangerous.
That's why...
As a man of the Takagi family,
I shall fulfill my obligation
to the retainer!
[crash]
So sorry, my baby is just...
[Soichiro] This is
the present we're facing!
And so, even if they're your
wonderful friends,
beloved family members and
people you once loved,
you must defeat them
without hesitation.
If you want to survive...
[Soichiro] You must fight!
[Takashi]
What's the matter, Hirano?
You don't look so well.
Swords are incredibly
inefficient.
What are you talking about?
I said they're inefficient!
The Japanese sword can break
if it hits bone.
It's useless after slicing
three or four people.
[Saeko] You can't say that
for sure, Hirano.
Even in the way of sword...
numbers determine your strength.
[Saeko]
The swordsman's technique,
the quality of his sword,
his mental strength...
If these three elements are at
high levels, you won't lose
your fighting strength,
no matter how many people you
have to fight against.
But once the sword has blood
on it, then it's impossible to‐
Hey, Hirano, that's enough.
Don't touch me!
[Kota] And don't interrupt me!
You can't even shoot
a gun properly!
Hirano, you need to back off!
Hey, Hirano!
[Saeko] One big happy family.
[Arisu] Takashi!
What's wrong? Did you have
a fight with Kota?
No, he and I just...
Yeah, I guess I did.
[Arisu] Okay then,
I'll tell you something good.
You need to talk to him again.
You just need to talk
to Kota some more
and then you guys can
figure out what's wrong.
So you think I can?
Sure, you can!
After everything that's happened
before we got here,
you two can't have a fight now!
After everything
that's happened...
You both have been too close
to be mad.
I'll tell him you want to talk!
Come on, Zero!
[Takashi]
Mutiny on the Bounty...
I was in 8th grade.
It was right before the
holiday weekend in the spring.
My homeroom teacher was
really into history,
talked about the story to us.
It was the last class
before the holiday.
In 1788, after a rough voyage,
a British military ship
named Bounty reached
the island of Tahiti,
the paradise in the
South Pacific Ocean.
The ship left Tahiti
after spending about
six months there.
Within a month after that,
a mutiny broke out.
After months in paradise, the
crew couldn't take the life
they once knew on the Bounty.
Our teacher made the
comparison of the
holiday weekend to Tahiti,
and us to the crew
of the Bounty.
I didn't understand what he
was talking about then.
I didn't care. None of us did.
It all makes sense to me now.
[Saya] Takashi!
Hurry up and come with me!
Kota...
Kota's in big trouble!
We have to go to him now!
[Saya] Where the hell did he go?
Jeez, he moves pretty fast
for a fat ass.
These German koi are
simply beautiful.
[Saeko] You don't get to see
this just anywhere.
It's quite unusual.
So, you're an expert in kendo,
and you have a part‐time
job at Petsmart?
You sound like you have it
all figured out.
[Saeko]
I'm good at a lot of things.
But how would you know
what I sound like?
[thud]
Guh! I won't do it!
[Kota] Give me a break!
Hand it over, fat boy!
Come on.
You know what's
going on out there.
You really shouldn't keep
a weapon like that
all to yourself.
You should give it to
someone who‐
I said no!
I'm borrowing these
from someone.
Besides, no one here can use
any of these weapons
better than I can!
[Saya] I don't mean to rain
on your parade, my little
Miss Life Aquatic.
But you have realized
what's happened?
That there are no more koi
ponds and kendo tournaments.
Things have changed.
Those days are over.
That's right...
The world that
we once enjoyed...
that world is long gone.
Go ahead...
You know what to do.
We don't have time
for this kid's whining!
Hirano!
[Saeko] So tell me,
you still have something
to get off your chest, do you?
I do.
I wanna know
where you stand on this.
Are you going to stay here with
them, or go out on our own?
[Soichiro]
What the hell is all this?
M‐Master!
He's just a kid, sir.
H‐He doesn't have any business
with these guns.
[Soichiro] I'm Soichiro Takagi,
former lord of Tokonosu,
the master of Tendo Sogon‐ryu!
What is your name, young man?
Ko‐Ko‐Kota Hirano!
I got to Fujimi Academy.
I'm in Class 2‐B,
roster number 32.
Something tells me
that you have spirit.
I'm quite sure that you went
through a lot before you made
it all the way here.
[Soichiro] I take it you
don't intend to hand over
your weapons?
N‐No, sir, I don't want to!
Without the gun,
I'm going right back
to the way I was before!
They'll make fun of me again!
I don't want to go back there!
I've finally figured out
what I can do!
What exactly can you do?
[Soichiro] Tell me!
Well I can...
I can... I can...
[Takashi] He can protect
your daughter, sir!
K‐Komuro...
Komuro? Interesting.
Yes, that name sounds
familiar to me.
You were friends with my
daughter since she was little,
were you not?
Yes sir, still am.
But Hirano has been the one
who's been protecting her.
We've all been
working together, sir.
He keeps the guns.
[Arisu] Kota!
I'll have you know, I've seen
his bravery with my own eyes.
[Saya] Me too, Daddy!
[Saya] He's just a
loser military otaku,
but without him I would've
been one of those zombies
by now, Daddy.
That's right!
He's the one who's been
protecting me!
He did your job!
Takagi... Thank you.
[Maruyama] Yes...
Yes, that's correct.
Right, getting ready to
get away from here.
If you ask for help now,
I'm sure they'll let you in.
They seem nice.
Mr. Shido!