[Yuriko] Get the ladder!
Get them out of there now!
[Takashi] Who are these people?
[Saeko] I don't think they're
from the fire department.
Mommy!
[Takashi]
That's Takagi's mother?
Fuckin' a! We're saved!
Not quite. I have a hard time
believe more help is really
on the way.
Well then, we go to them.
Come on. I know this area.
I'll be waiting!
Come to my house on the hill!
Damn it, this place too?
It doesn't look like we can
make it to the second block.
[Takashi]
Let's go back the way we came.
We didn't run into any of Them
on the way here.
[Takashi] I can see
Takagi's house from here.
[Saeko] Are you ready to walk
on the fence again?
[Takashi] No way.
Man, if I only had a bike...
Check it out!
[Takashi] I'll pick our ride.
You get what you think we need.
[Saeko] That's fine,
but tandem is dangerous.
This isn't a date, right?
[nervous laughter]
[Saeko] How about this?
[Takashi] Oh hell yeah!
That's what I'm talkin' about.
Did I ever tell you how much
I like your taste?
Things are about to
get interesting.
Yeah, you got that right.
I don't suppose you have a plan?
Feel like sharing it with me?
I do!
But...
You do but what?
It might get a little
too interesting.
Don't worry...
What you give me, I can handle.
[Takashi] Hold on tight!
They can use the stairs but
can't walk on a slope?
Appears so.
[Saeko]
But their recovery is flawless.
It's not going to matter at all.
Really?
And what makes you think that?
[Takashi]
Cuz if that's the case...
What the hell?
What are you doing?
This thing's amphibious!
Amphibious?
Oh shit! Sorry Saeko! You okay?
[Takashi] Uh, oh Go...
Geez! You don't have to stare!
[Takashi] Uh... I know!
I‐I'm sorry!
Oh come on now, don't tell me
that took it all out of you.
W‐What do you mean?!
N‐No! I swear I'm good to go!
Maybe you should use your
bedroom voice.
[Saeko] It was a clever idea
to use the sandbar.
[Takashi]
You know, when I was a kid,
I was told over and over
again never to play here
because the water is too deep
and the current was too strong.
Well, whether it worked out
as you planned or not,
it's nice to have a break.
[Takashi] Yeah, let's take turns
and watch out for Them.
I'll watch first. You go ahead
and take a break, Saeko.
[sneeze]
Ex‐Excuse me.
I'm freezing my ass off here.
Yeah, sorry about that.
[Takashi]
Here, wear this for now.
Thank you.
[Saeko] I'm done.
What's wrong? Don't you like it?
No! Not at all, just the
opposite actually...
God you're such a sucker.
Can't you tell when I'm
just fucking with you?
You're what?!
Oh yeah, I'm sorry.
Sorry...
[Saeko] No reason to apologize.
[Takashi] Uh... Hey.
Let me ask you, have you ever
had a boyfriend or something?
[Saeko] Excuse me?
[Takashi] Uh, I'm just trying
to make conversation...
I mean...
Someone like you maybe...
crush at least?
Of course I have...
I almost thought it was love.
[Saeko] I guess it's okay now.
Looks like most of
Them are gone.
[Takashi] Oh, yeah.
Now I see more.
Seems like you and I get more
popular by the minute.
We'll find out after turning
the next corner.
A park?
Oh come on, don't you like
merry‐go‐rounds?
Jesus Christ! Do you
actually enjoy getting
me wet or something?!
Just give me the tape
from the backpack.
[Saeko] Huh. Not too bad...
Lure Them with the noise
and then...
Very nice.
[Takashi] If we go through
the east exit,
it'll put us right behind
Takagi's house.
I'd rather not use the gun
because the sound echoes,
but you never know...
All right then...
We'll do this!
Hold it.
God you reek.
I know you're dead, but is a
little hygiene too much to ask?
Now then...
That's enough holding back!
Holy shit, she's a maniac.
What are you doing?
Why'd you stop?
Saeko!
What the hell's going on?
Come on!
[Takashi] Hurry up!
Saeko, tell me
what happened back there.
It's too dangerous for us
to be out at night.
We wait here until morning.
[Takashi] Whoa, this is real.
Saeko, look at this...
[Takashi]
Come here and have a seat.
Your uniform is dry too.
I'm done.
What a relief.
Look what I found, Saeko.
What do you mean? Found what?
[Takashi] Wanna know what?
Here it is.
It's some kind of porta‐potty.
You can have it.
Why are you laughing at me?
I'd figured you'd find it
quite handy, so...
[Saeko] No, you're right.
Thank you...
Thanks a lot.
[Saeko]
So, you're not going to ask?
[Takashi]
For you to act that way...
I guess it was something
very serious.
If you don't mind, I just
want to talk about it...
You brought it up after all.
[Saeko]
I started thinking about it...
the fear.
Because you saw the little kids?
Is that it?
To tell you the truth, it wasn't
about them at all.
Remember you asked me, at the
sandbar, if I've ever had a
crush on someone?
Oh yeah, about that‐ I'm sorry.
[Saeko] It's okay.
I mean, hasn't everyone?
Can't get this far without
having a crush...
on someone...
[Saeko]
I've never told them how I felt.
I just don't think I have
the right to.
[Takashi] But I think you can
get anyone you want.
[Saeko] Even though I almost
killed someone?
[Saeko] Four years ago,
I was attacked on the street
at night.
I had a practice sword with me.
I started hitting him and once
I started...
I didn't stop.
I‐I couldn't stop.
It was... he was...
After I told the police
what happened,
they gave me a ride home
in the police car.
[Takashi]
But it was just self‐defense...
[Saeko] It might've started out
that way, but to be honest...
I enjoyed it...
Just letting the rage out
against someone?
That was nothing but joy.
[Saeko] When I realized
I had the upper hand,
I felt so calm and
I pretended I was terrified.
And then when I had him...
I fought back.
I fought him until there was
nothing but blood and bones.
It was bliss.
Absolute, total pleasure.
That's me! Me!
That's who I am! Can't you see?
[Saeko]
The feeling of power, of control
over someone else's life.
I loved it!
Does anyone like that
deserve love?
But ever since this has
happened, I've felt
that way too!
You became that way after
this happened...
But I was like that before.
Don't say that.
Nothing about me has changed.
I realized that in front of
the fountain.
[Saeko] Almost feels like
it's gotten worse.
We'll get to the street
from the back.
We should be able to get to
Takagi's house in twenty
minutes by foot.
[Takashi] Why are they here?
We didn't make any noise.
God damn it.
I don't understand.
Saeko, I say we make
a run for it!
[Takashi] Saeko!
I can't do it.
Stop...
Wh‐What are you doing?
Don't even think for a minute
you're quitting on me now!
You got it?
We've come too far. There's no
way we're giving up!
To die like this, have these
dead motherfuckers take us
down here?!
[Takashi] It's not going to
happen! You're coming with me!
Because whether you like
it or not,
I need you!
Maybe that son of a bitch
deserved to die, who knows?
I don't give a shit what
you did before!
I just care about what
you do now!
Thank you, I'm okay now.
What are you waiting for?
Let's go.
This is it!
This is me!
Saeko!
Yes!
[Takashi] Saeko, this way!
W‐What a minute.
You meant what you
said, right?
[Takashi] Hells yeah!
[Arisu] Why are we in the back?
I have a feling they'd
come through the back
if they wanted to sneak in.
[barking]
Zero?
It's Takashi!
[Saya] Open the gate.
[servant] Yes, ma'am!
[barking]
[Arisu] You're back!
You're both back!
[Takashi] I accepted it.
I accepted her darkness.
Why wouldn't I?
I mean, I needed her
to be that way.
The darker she was, the more
chance I had to survive.