[bang]
[reporter] The so‐called
"killing pandemic"
that's been occuring all
over the world continues to
spread with unprecedented speed.
The number of the patients of
this killing pandemic in our
country has already reached
over two million.
[growling]
[reporter] Because of its
powerful infectiousness and the
paralyzed system,
it's speculated that the number
could reach ten million within
a day or two.
And centers for disease control
appear to be stymied.
[Saya] Are you looking at me?
[Rei] Oh come on, don't be
such a prude.
[reporter] ...in an effort to
keep the station on the air,
have decided to take the
broadcasting team to an
undisclosed offshore facility.
[reporter] Unfortunately,
this is going to be the
last broadcasting as a
scheduled program.
[Saya] Come on!
[Shizuka] Miss Miyamoto!
[Rei] Hurry up!
[reporter] Goodbye, everyone,
and good luck.
It feels nice.
[Shizuka] It feels like I'm
melting away!
This is shampoo, right?
[Rei] Good God, you're gigantic!
I know, I get that a lot.
Almost impossibly gigantic.
[Rei] Here! Let me see those
things. They can't be real!
[Shizuka] Ah! Stop it
Miss Miyamoto!
Oh no! No, they're‐ oh!
Give me a break!
[Rei] Wait a minute, they don't
feel fake.
[Saya] Good God.
[Saya] So, what? We all just had
to take a bath at the same time?
But you know why, don't
you, Takagi?
Yeah, I guess so.
[Saya] But considering the
current situation that we
are in,
I don't think we should be
doing stuff like this.
[shriek]
[Saeko] That voice is better
than I thought it would be.
Boys must love your sexy voice.
Ah!
[Saya] Don't look at me like
that, you're the one who
started it.
[giggling]
[Takashi] Sounds like they're
having fun.
[Kota] You want to go have
a peek?
You know we're supposed to,
right?
I don't want to die just yet.
[Takashi] And I'm gonna be
really pissed off if there's
nothing in here.
[Kota] There has to be.
We found the ammunition,
so there has to be something
in here.
[Takashi] Oh well,
it doesn't matter.
Let's do it!
[in unison] One...
...two, three!
Man...
[Takashi] Hello!
What?
[crazed laughter]
I just knew it!
[Takashi] So she lives here
with a friend of hers,
isn't that right?
Who is she? Sarah fucking Palin?
[sneeze]
[Tajima] What's the matter?
[Rika] Someone's talking
about me.
[Tajima] What?
Not a lot of friends,
so it's probably...
Springfield M1A1, Super Match.
It's semi‐automatic,
but the M14 series'
full‐automatic is nothing but
a waste of bullets anyway.
Uh, chill out dude.
I can put twenty bullets in
the magazine!
That's illegal in Japan.
Illegal!
[laughter]
Hello, Hirano!
[Kota] Knights SR‐25 rifle!
No, you can't get that in Japan,
so they just completely
modified an AR110?
[Kota] What's left in the locker
is a crossbow.
It's a descendent of the one
Robin Hood used.
Barnett Wildcat C5!
Made in Britain, you can even
kill a bear with it!
That's an eetha M37
riot shotgun!
It's a super‐sick shotgun made
by Americans!
It played a big part in the
Vietnam War too!
I see...
Are you nuts?! Don't point a
thing like that at anyone even
unloaded, but when you do...
shoot to kill.
Roger that.
I hope that's the only thing
I need to point at.
You know...
If it comes down to something
like that...
If I happen to get bit, don't
you think twice about blasting
my head off.
Yeah, same here.
It's a deal!
[Saeko] Ow!
[Rei] God, more big ones!
Will you help too, Komuro?
It's a pain in the butt to put
the bullets in.
Did you practice with
airsoft guns?
No way, with the real ones.
What are you saying?
You've done this before?
When I went to America...
[Kota] I was trained by
this instructor,
who used to work for a private
military company, Black Water,
for a month.
He's an ex‐captain of
Delta Force.
Oh my God, the class nerd's
a card carrying member of
the N. R. A.
I'm really glad we're
on the same side.
Yeah.
[Takashi] And if that's your
secret life, what's this
chick's deal?
These guns are definitely
illegal, aren't they?
It's legal to purchase the
guns and parts.
But it is illegal if you put
them together in this way.
Whoever lives here definitely
knows what they're doing.
And that makes sense to me since
Miss Shizuka said her roommate
used to be in the military.
So you can get away with
anything as long as
you're a cop.
[Kota] It's obvious the person
isn't an ordinary citizen.
An unmarried police officer
usually lives in the dormitory,
but to think this person is
renting a room like this...
Either her parents are rich,
or the man she's dating is rich,
or she's involved with some
funny business.
They should probably hold it
down in there.
[Takashi] It's okay.
I know they respond to what
they hear, but they're not
hearing the girls...
If they are infected,
keep your distance from them!
[cop] I repeat, if they show
signs of infection,
keep far from them!
No one who is injured or shows
signs of infection...
[reporter] The lockdown of the
west area of Tokonosu city is
still in effect.
However, as this killing
pandemic has continued to
spread throughout the world,
some people are strongly
criticizing the lockdown,
questioning the necessity
of it.
We came here to report on
this story, however, due to
this pandemic,
we haven't been able to return
to the headquarters,
which has been relocated
on the ocean.
So as long as it's possible,
we'll continue to bring
you coverage.
What do you mean we're free
to do whatever?
[captain] What about the
backup from the
Prefectural Headquarters?
All communication has
been cut off?
God damn it!
Captain, at this rate,
they're going to break
through the barricade.
Can't say I blame them.
We're too short‐handed. For
Christ's sake, they brought
in people from accounting.
[officer] What do we do?
[captain] We've got a message
from upper management.
They said we're allowed to
do anything in order to
maintain order.
Supposedly, things are crazy
down there too.
The last order that they
received from headquarters...
was to do whatever they could
do to control this mob.
Then, give us an order now!
If there are unharmed citizens
on the bridge or the other side,
we should sacrifice a small
group in order to save the
larger group!
[captain] How ironic. Our job is
to protect these people...
And you watch!
Now we're going to be forced
to kill most of them!
[Takashi] I'm getting sick.
Here, I've had enough.
This reminds me of that scene
in Apocalypse Now.
Huh? What's that?
[Takashi] What is it?
[Kota] Turn on the TV.
Don't tolerate the tyranny
of the police department!
[crowd] Don't tolerate it!
[protestor] We strongly condemn
this biological weapon,
this circulation of killing
pandemic developed by our
government and America!
Just now, this group, which is
protesting against the lockdown
of the bridge, has started
their demonstration.
As you can see, tensions here
are running extremely high!
Killing pandemic?
I guess they're talking
about Them.
We don't know what kind
of group it is.
According to the flyer
distributed by the group,
the main focus of their protest
is to condemn those who allowed
this killing pandemic to spread.
[reporter] It sounds like
they believe that the
biological weapon‐
Are they serious?
What? Biological weapon?!
[Takashi] They know damn well no
kind of science can explain...
why dead corpses walk
around eating people!
You know this is just some
government propaganda.
Maybe the media‐
[bang]
I didn't say you could shoot!
Stop it!
Stop shooting!
She's still alive!
My girl is still alive!
[lady] Pl..Please...
My baby... my baby...
[lady] Help her!
[protestor]
See what they've done?!
You see?!
They're killing off
citizens at random!
Don't tolerate the tyranny
of the police!
[protestor] If we allow them to
shoot one of us‐
Hey, shoot that guy. Just do it!
[crowd] Don't tolerate it!
Don't tolerate it!
[captain] You must
leave immediately.
[protestor] Fuck off! What?
I'm afraid it's too dangerous
for you to be here.
Oh is it?!
Any more dangerous than
the government?!
Your conspiracies?!
I'll ask one more time.
You need to disband and go.
Hell no!
You go!
[crowd]
Go home! Go home! Go home!
You don't seem to understand,
my friend. I've been given
strict orders to maintain
public safety...
by any means necessary...
by whatever means I see fit...
Huh?
[screaming]
Oh man. This is insane...
Holy shit.
We need to get the fuck
outta here.
No way, Takashi! We can't
leave now. They could attack
us in the dark.
Sorry about that!
Okay look lady, this is not
the time...
Don't be like that.
It's just a little kiss.
[Shizuka] See?
[Takashi] Hey!
Kota, darling!
Me? "Darling"?
Me? Ooh!
Good boy, good boy,
so you want a prize?
We should keep it down!
Please go downstairs.
No! No way!
I'm going to stay right here
just like this!
Oh, I'm so tired, I might just
pass out...
Miss Shizuka?
I'm so sleepy.
You know, you could help
me out here.
Uh, I like turtles.
Okay, here we go. Hold on tight.
Hey wait!
You're touching my butt!
You're naughty, Komuro.
Such a bad boy!
Naugthy...
If this was any other time or
any other place, this would be
so fuckin' hot.
Am I interrupting anything?
[Takashi] No...
You're not
interrupting anything...
[Rei] Hmm?
[Takashi] But if this
was another time...
[Rei] Hey, you look really
good in threes!
[Takashi] I'm what?
All of a sudden there's
a bunch of you!
Oh come on, not you too?
[Rei]
I guess I'm just exhausted.
I can't believe it's
only been one day.
I can't get a hold of
my mom or dad and...
Hisashi is dead too.
[sobbing]
[snoring]
[Saeko] Komuro?
Late‐night snack will
be ready soon.
[Saeko] And tomorrow's
lunch too.
Man, I love girls' apartments.
Everything's so sta‐
[Takashi] Stocked!
I‐I mean stocked!
What's wrong?
Uh... W‐What? N‐Nothing!
Oh, so you mean this old thing?
Yeah, terrible isn't it?
[Saeko] I couldn't find a size
that fits me so until I finish
doing laundry I'm wearing this.
But I guess it's a
little too revealing.
Oh, no, it's okay, I hadn't
noticed a titt‐ a thing!
We should be prepared.
They could come attit‐ attack.
You and Hirano are watching out
for us and that's sweet.
I want you to know how much
that means to me, Takashi.
[Saeko] I mean, I really
want you to know. Really.
Hey Takashi! Come up here!
[Rei] Come up here!
[Saeko] You'd better pay
attention to her.
At times, a girl likes to,
well, pretend to be helpless.
[Takashi] Do you, Miss Busujima?
[Saeko] I want to be called
"Saeko" by my friends.
Sa..Sa...
You can call me that
after practicing.
[Rei] Come on! Get up here!
Takashi! Takashi!
[Rei] He was always so
nice to me!
He paid attention to me.
I mean, when we went to kareoke,
he really got into it.
He didn't just sit there and
play Bubble Popper on his phone.
When I was lonely, he was always
there to listen to me.
[Rei] Even about me repeating
the same grade...
All you ever do is get upset
about it, but...
Yeah.
Hey, are you listening?
I'm just tired.
[Takashi] I'm tired, that's all.
What the hell is that?
See what I mean?
You're just boring.
Well yeah, I guess that's
probably why you dumped me.
There are always two‐
[Takashi] ...sides to
every story?
Would've been nice if you
ever heard my side.
It would've been nice to hear
it. At least Hisashi talked
to me.
Shut up!
I swear to God, you bring up
Hisashi every chance you can!
I'm not him!
[Takashi] Besides...
he's dead!
If anybody knows that, I do!
Just face the facts will you?
He's not coming back.
We're still alive, both of us.
Want to stay that way?!
I do! So why don't you stop
bringing it‐
[worker] A‐Are you serious?
We'll take total responsibility.
Just do it now!
[worker] You've got to be
kidding me...
[engine rev]
Die, all of you!
God damn it! I can't believe
they just abandoned all of
us here like that!
Get back! It's coming this way!
[officer] That's right,
we'll bring back the bulldozer
once you reach the middle of
the bridge.
And we do have permission to
shoot whoever enters the area!
Hang on, let me ask
the commander...
[gunshot]
[Takashi] Stop.
If you keep this up, well...
You know...
[giggling]
[barking]
Is that a dog barking?
Even now, some things
never change.
But it sounds close.
Hira‐ What?
Bad news, man.
[barking]
[Takashi] They kept coming.
It seemed like everywhere
we went, they followed.
Their hunger, it never ended.
They never ended.