(battle cries)
No matter how many
times I try to shake him off,
he comes charging
right back!
She's not laying down that
much fire, so here goes!
I'm not done yet!
Hyaaa!
Yah!
AAAAHHHH!!!
Heh. Not bad.
You're going down
this time, Rinin!
The first training battle
of the second term...
These two seem very
enthusiastic.
Uh‐huh.
And once again, Orimura is the
dominant one in the battle.
No... that reckless idiot
has no strategy at all.
Rin... the next round
ends this.
(battle cry)
What?!
Gotcha! YAAAH!!
(pained scream)
Rinin:
Your shield
energy's all gone!
(chuckles)
Gasp!
(buzzer sounds)
(sighs)
I was so close to
winning that match.
I'm gonna have to do something
about my fuel consumption‐ Uh!
Tatenashi:
Guess who!
Uh, uh, huh?!
Who the heck is that?!
Tatenashi:
Too late! Guessing
time's over.
(giggles)
I got ya, huh?
Yeah... who are you?
Well, see ya later!
By the way, you're going to be
in trouble with Miss Orimura
if you don't hurry
it up now (tisks).
Huh?
WAAAAHH!
Chifuyu:
So...
That's your excuse for
being so late?
Well, basically, there was
this mysterious blue‐haired girl
who I'd never met before
and she was, uh...
So you were late
for my class,
because you prioritized
a conversation with a girl
you didn't even know?
That's... not
what I said!
Dunois...! Please
demonstrate the rapid switch!
The what?!
Now... observe the rapid switch.
(cowers)
Um, hold on... can we talk,
Charlotte, buddy, ol' pal?
Is something wrong, Orimura?
Let us begin... revive go!
Ichika:
AAAAAAAAAAAHHHH!
Sigh...
PA Announcer:
Ladies and GentleMAN
of the IS Academy.
Standby for an address
from the president
of your student council.
Hm...?
Hmm... things have been
hectic this year,
so hectic, that many of you
haven't properly met me yet!
Tatenashi:
My name's
Tatenashi Sarashiki.
And if you're in this student
body, that makes me your head.
(giggles)
Our annual school festival
is coming up.
That means each class must
decide what they want to do
as a fundraising project.
(giggles)
Good luck!
Ichika:
Okay... the suggestions
handed in for our class'
program fundraiser are...
Ichika:
(horrifed groans)
...all rejected!
Whaaaat?!
Are you nuts...! Who would wanna
do ANY of that kinda stuff?!
I'm absolutely sure
I would! No doubt!
Ichika:
WHAT?!
Tanimoto's right!
You should follow through with
your duty to please us!
Ichika:
B‐but!
Yeah, Ichika Orimura
is public property!
(angry agreement)
Miss Yamada, you wouldn't
actually approve any of these
ludicrous ideas, would you?
Actually...
From... the suggestions
I've seen so far,
I think I'd prefer
the one with the Pocky.
What I mean is, we need to do
something more normal!
Perhaps the maid cafe?
Student:
Oh yeah. Right on!
Maid cafe, Laura?
I'm sure it would be well
received...
Und besides, an eatery will
let you earn back the money
you spend on it.
Hm...
That's a good one...
Not only that, we can have
Ichika either helping out
in the kitchen,
or he could
be a butler.
Huh?
Student:
Orimura as a butler?
That sounds totally awesome!
We need costumes.
I know how to sew.
Okay, so we've settled
on the café idea?
I agree!
Students:
(buzzing in agreement)
Well, I guess I can
just pretend it's a café
with some unusual outfits.
Oh, no! It's already time
for my special training!
Ah‐ah‐ah!
Hi there!
Right... student council
president, of course.
Oh, don't be so formal.
Just call me Tatenashi.
Uh‐huh. And what
do you want?
Oh, what I want, is to be
your very personal IS coach.
Huh?!
Hold on, this is
totally out of the blue!
I already have so many coaches,
I don't need a new one!
If you have so many, then why
is your performance so weak?
Well that's rather personal, and
I don't think I'm all that weak!
Oh, yes, you are...
Totally limp in the saddle.
Therefore, in order to make you
just a teensy‐peensy bit better,
I'm going to be your
personal trainer for now.
I'll tell you what
Miss Rude‐and‐Bossy,
let's settle this IS style!
We fight, and the winner
tells the loser what to do!
Sure! Sounds fun!
The rules are if you're able to
get me down on the ground even
once, you're the winner.
Huh?
Tatenashi:
However...
for me to win,
I must render you
unable to continue.
Are you okay with that?
You sure do like to
underestimate me, don't you?
(chuckles)
Oh, I'm not
underestimating anything.
All right...
I won't hold back.
Less talking,
more attacking.
(battle cry)
Tatenashi:
You see, at the IS Academy,
the title of student
council (grunt) president...
stands as proof of one
very important fact.
You see, the council
president by default...
is the head of
the whole student body.
Tatenashi:
And must, therefore,
be the strongest fighter!
Got it?
That's three in a row...
are you done yet?
I'm not done yet!
Hm...!
I do like a boy
with stamina...
That's nice to know.
(battle stance)
Uh!
AHHH!
Ah! You're a pervert!
(stammers)
Uh... sorry!
The thing is...
there's a price to seeing
a girl's lingerie...
and you're gonna pay!
Tatenashi:
WITH INTEREST!
Ichika:
AAAAAAAAAAAAAHHH!
Where in the devil could he
have gotten to this time...?
He is the worst bride ever!
Is it possible that Ichika
is trying to avoid me...?
Ach, nein.
(giggling)
Oh, hey... I just
noticed that you have a
major cowlick going on
No! Where
is it? Gosh!
I overslept this morning,
so I didn't have much time
to fix my hair!
That's not cool.
You have to keep your
appearance up or Orimura
isn't going to notice you.
Appearance?
There!
Chifuyu:
Oh...
So you worry about stuff
like that now, do you?
Huh?!
Heh. I guess you're that age.
Uh... It's not what
it looks like, Mentor!
You may think I'm being
frivolous, but I'm‐
Oooh!
That's "Miss Orimura"
to you.
Jawohl.
I just saw Orimura...
he was in front of
the club building's infirmary.
Huh? "The Infirmary"?
Oh...
(whispers)
Are you awake?
Huh?!
WHOAAAAAA!
Uh, what the hell
is going on here?!
You're lying down.
That's not what I
was talking abo‐OW!
There, there. Take it easy.
Hmm?!
Uh...
(giggles)
This target shall
now be destroyed.
You're dead!
Whoa!
Now that's a good girl.
Tatenashi:
All right, Ichika!
Are you ready to get started?
Ichika:
Uh, okay.
Hold on, that's Ichika!
I don't
understand...
I could have sworn that he was
getting special training from
Laura in Arena Four.
Hello, girls! I'll be
taking over as Ichika's
exclusive coach from now on.
Nice to meet you!
The council president
is his coach?
Just hold on!
What's going on, Ichika?
Mm‐hm!
Well, I kinda... lost a
contest we just had and...
Don't worry! This is all in
Ichika's best interest.
But, there is something that
I'll need to get you ladies
to help me with.
You need us?
To help?
Uh...
We're running short on time,
so let's get this started.
Charlotte, Cecilia, demonstrate
the proper shooter flow
for a circle
rondo formation.
Cecilia:
Hmm... do you suppose a
fire‐based battle stance
would be helpful
to Ichika at all?
(sighs)
Right! Here we go!
Cecilia:
Ichika be sure you're
paying close attention
to all my magnificent moves,
alright?
En garde, Cecilia!
Do your worst,
you villain!
That's incredible!
They're firing while
also executing advanced
manual frame control.
Tatenashi:
And, in addition...
they're also maintaining focus
on evasion and targeting.
Is that... understood?
AAH! Why're you there?!
Gasp! Ichika!
What are they doing down there?!
That is totally inapproriate!
Are you guys... okay?
Alright, Ichika,
now it's your turn.
Ready yourself, Ichika!
Ready or not, here I come!
Oh yeah... sure.
Jeez... This is
really different...
Hmm! Not bad!
Now let's see your guns!
Charl:
Ichika!
Ichika, dearest,
are you all right?
Uh, yeah, just peachy.
Let's keep going, Cecilia.
Well, I'm not in the mood,
but if you really want to get
back in the saddle, then...
One more time!
Is this because of the
Byakushiki recent augmentation
for long‐range
assault capabilities?
Yes...
that's correct...
But actually that's
not the only thing.
Tatenashi:
In order for firepower
to be effective,
it needs wide
distribution, right?
But even at maximum output,
a charged‐particle gun
isn't capable of rapid fire, so
it's more like a sniper rifle.
So... it's about
one lethal shot.
Given how poor Ichika's
shooting skills obviously are...
he really has to improve...
therefore...
You made him fight
at close range.
Right... you're sharp!
Whooooaaaaa...!
(sighs)
I'm beat...
Tatenashi:
Welcome home, dear!
Hm...? Huh?!
Would you like dinner...?
Or to take a bath...?
Or perhaps... to‐have‐me?
Silly boy!
I was just asking...
would you like,
to‐have‐me.
What the hell do you think
you're doing in here?!
Huh?!
Well... since I'm
your special coach...
I wanted us to
become synchronized...
by eating and
sleeping together.
Well... actually,
I... don't...
Surprise! It's
just a swimsuit!
Oh, Ichika, your
reaction is so cute!
(giggle‐laughs)
Tatenashi:
(giggling)
Ichika:
Yes, who is it?
It's just me...
I've brought some food
for you, Ichika.
Is it alright
if I come in?
Ichika:
Houki! Uh, sorry,
not right now!
Tatenashi:
Ichika! What are you doing?
Oh, I get it!
You're dying not to let her know
that you're messing around
in here, right?
Why you!
Houki:
Ichika! How dare you!
As if it's not bad enough to
sneak a girl into your room,
but you're also doing something
in here that's totally indecent!
Know your shame!
Wait, wait! You've got
it all wrong!
Huh?!
Uh‐uh, Houki... I'm sorry,
but I can't let you
kill Ichika right now...
because that would be a
little inconvenient for me.
What the‐?!
Game over! Bye!
Your inertial coordinates
are off‐center. Correct now.
Yeah, right!
So Ichika, do you always yield
to your elders so easily?
Not that easily!
Tatenashi:
Your velocity is declining!
You need to maintain focus!
Right, understood!
Okay... I see you've
increased your speed...
And now I want you to attempt
to engage the ignition boost.
Ichika:
You want me to what?
The ignition boost.
Tatenashi:
You have to shift from the
shooter flow's circular orbit
to a straight‐line.
Then penetrate your
opponent's line of fire
and use the charged‐particle gun
at point‐blank range!
Ichika:
Hold on! I can't just
do something like that
all of a sudden!
Engage!
Gasp! Oh what the hell!
That... hurt...
Here's a tip. You must
always remember not to interrupt
the shooter flow
while you're charging.
Yeah, sure... simple.
Tatenashi:
Come on. You need
to learn how to do this.
So, get back up
and try it again.
Right.
Um... Ichika, are you okay?
Uh... define "okay"...
Have some tea...
If you can't
eat anything,
you should at
least drink some tea.
Oh... thank you, Charl...
And what happened to that
blue‐haired floosey?
She said she had some student
council business to attend to...
I guess it was your fault
for rising to her stupid
provocation to begin with.
But still, she didn't have
to beat you up this badly.
Yeah, well, I probably just
got what I deserved.
It's like
Miss Tatenashi said ‐
Ichika:
I am still really weak
in certain areas,
and I need to master those
skills as soon as possible.
You know...
when I see a boy
who is doing his best,
That is
a wonderful thing.
I have to agree...
You're doing a lot better now.
Ahem... Ichika... if you
happen to find the conditions of
your present room to
be less than desirable,
I'm certain I could find
it in my heart to permit you
to be a guest in my
quarters.
Hey, wait just a
second there, missy!
Ichika, I think you ought
to come stay in my room!
I have playing cards!
Hold on! I have the
playing cards in my room.
How about hanafuda
cards, Ichika?
I forgot to mention it, but I
have tarot cards in my room!
Shh!
(Ichika snoring)
Huh?
Houki:
No one is around, right? Good.
Ichika, I like you.
I‐I like you, Ichika!
Ichika, will you please
make me some miso soup?
Ichika, meow, I like
you a lot, meow.
Ah! Um, Miss Chifuyu?!
Chifuyu:
Next time on Infinite Stratos 2,
Translucent Chord of
Cinderella's Heel.
Houki:
Meow...