(Computer beeps and motors whir)
[KANZASHI]
None of the drive sections
are responding properly.
But why?
And the core's aptitude level...
Why isn't rising?
Am I using the wrong type?
Uh...
Sigh...
Forget this.
I'm gonna watch some anime.
Yoohoo, Orimura and Shinonono.
Hey Mayuzumi.
How's the newspaper going?
Well, I've got a favor
to ask of you.
A favor...
to ask me and Ichika?
That's right.
My older sister is working
at a publishing company now,
and I was wondering if...
maybe she could
interview the two of you
since you each have
your own IS units.
Oh, this is the magazine.
Um, this doesn't have anything
to do with IS units, does it?
Hold on. Have neither
of you done any of this
kind of work before?
No...
[MAYUZUMI]
Well, some pilots with
their own IS units
are kind of like celebrities.
There's some tech stuff,
but more about fashion shoots
and modeling and stuff.
Wha‐? Is that right, Houki?
Uh, why are you
asking me that?!
[RININ]
Are you talking about modeling?
Let me show you my portfolio.
Rin!
Uh, no... that's okay.
And why not?!
Well, isn't it you
just doing some kind of
weird poses and stuff?
What do you mean by weird?
Just take a look at them
and find out for yourself!
Look at them RIGHT NOW!
Huh...?
Oh, not bad.
Haha! I told you so, didn't I?
Oh, and have a look at this
one from that summer event
we attended last year.
(School bell)
Hey, tell you what,
I'll catch ya after class.
And then check
this one out, it's‐
Ow, that hurt!
Someone needs to go
back to Class Two.
Yes, Ma'am...
[CHIFUYU]
Now then...
For today's lecture,
I'd like to begin by discussing
the philosophy of close combat,
including implementing
effective evasive maneuvers
and how to keep your distance.
[GIRL]
Hey, have you heard
about the upcoming event
that's just for people
with personal IS units?
[OTHER GIRL]
What? Seriously?
Yeah, and I've heard
that Kanzashi from
our class is going.
Is she really?
But I thought that her
personal IS hadn't
been completed yet.
Yeah, I hope she
gets it done in time.
(Exertions)
Um, Houki?
What?
The interview with Mayuzumi's
sister... Are you going?
No way...
It's against my principles
to be on display like an object.
[ICHIKA]
Yeah, that's what I
thought you'd say that.
Yo. Thanks for waiting!
Now down to business,
about the interview...
Well, about that, Houki
actually feels we‐
Oh, yeah. Did I mention
that the deal also includes
these dinner tickets to
a three‐star restaurant?
For two, of course.
I, uh...
I hate to say this bu‐
‐ We'll both do it!
‐ Huh?!
Well then, it's decided.
The interview's going
to be this Sunday.
‐ Uh, but we were...
‐ Thanks again! Bye bye!
Houki, what about
your principles?
Well, upon reflection,
it turns out that I happen to be
a person who's thinking
can be very flexible.
You mean twisted.
Do you have a
problem with that?
Well, no problem.
I guess I'm okay with doing it
as long as you're okay with it.
That's right...
Ahem... In regards..
to this free dinner tickets...
We are going
together, aren't we?
Sure. Why not?
They're going to interview
both of us after all.
Really?
I mean right...
You're totally right!
(Anime girl struggles)
You'd better tell me
where he is!
No, I won't!
Fine! We'll do it the hard way!
[HERO]
‐ That's far enough!
‐ Ah! What?!
There's nothing to be afraid of.
Just leave it to me.
[KANZASHI]
Someday...
Someone will come for me.
Who'll be a hero...
[BAD GUY]
Who do you think you are‐
Ugh!
[HERO]
Are you okay?
[ANIME GIRL]
Thanks to you.
[HERO]
I'm glad.
[KANZASHI]
A hero of my own. Who will
protect me and watch over me.
Hi there.
I'm Nagisako Mayuzumi,
the assistant editor of
"Infinite Stripes".
Thanks for coming.
Hi, I'm...
Ichika Orimura.
I'm Houki Shinonono.
Right.
If you don't mind, I'd like to
start with the interview first.
So, here's the first question.
Orimura, what's it like
attending an all‐girl school?
Well, uh...
it's difficult to find a
bathroom that I can use.
(Chuckle)
I guess what my sister's
been telling me is true!
Oh, yeah...
And now, Miss Shinonono,
there are some questions
about your sister that
I would like to ask.
(Grunt)
You received your personal IS
directly from her?
Is this a plan to make you
a representative contender?
[HOUKI]
About the Akatsubaki...
I'm grateful that she
gave it to me.
However...
I'm not interested in being
a representative
contender right now.
There have been offers,
but I have said no.
Okay, okay...
Now be honest,
between the two of you,
which one of you is
the strongest pilot?
That'd be me!
[NAGISAKO]
Oh, really?
Well, uh... yeah...
Oh, my. That's a bad thing
for you, as a hero, isn't it?
But I'm not trying to be
any kind of hero, Ma'am...
In the end, I'm just a
rank‐and‐file soldier.
Hey! I really like that line.
Okay, so if you were in command,
what's your
battlefield philosophy?
Well.. it's, uh...
Hmm...
to protect... my comrades!
Oh!
(Gasp)
Yes! That sounds so cool!
Okay, let's move on
to the photo shoot.
Oh...
I must protect Houki!
Yes!
Oh, yes! Yes! Yes!
(Giggle)
Uh!
I'm supposed to wear THIS?
Me?! You're kidding me!
On the other hand,
you know what?
Opportunity could be
knocking here.
Oh, yeah!
[FEMALE STAFF]
Thank you for waiting.
Miss Shinonono is ready now!
Oh!
Whoa!
I‐Ichika...
were you waiting long?
Um, uh‐huh...
You...
look good in that...
I mean... it's not...
not too bad.
Oh, thank you...
And you look...
awesome yourself, Houki.
(Gasp)
[HOUKI]
Ichika complimented me!
Right! Let's get this
photo shoot started!
[NAGISAKO]
Oh... hmm....
I need you to get closer, now.
Much closer.
Oh. Okay...
So, like this?
No. That's not good.
Get closer!
Okay.
Oh...
Great! I want this to have
a more mature feel.
Okay, next shot.
Orimura, hold Shinonono's waist.
Hm...
What?!
I‐said‐to‐hold‐her‐waist!
So, do it!
Ah! Yes, Ma'am!
Mmm, well, you heard her...
Uh...
(Deep breath)
(Gasp)
Uh...
[NAGISAKO]
Oh, nice! Nice. Very nice.
Okay, next shot.
Now, Shinonono, put your arm
around Orimura's neck.
Come on, get to it.
Chop, chop. Go, go.
(Gasp)
(Nervous breathing)
Mm...! These are some hot shots!
Oh! Um!
Uh, well, that was...
Yeah, that was...
[NAGISAKO]
Good job, guys.
You can keep the outfits.
Thank you so much
for everything today.
[FEMALE STAFF]
Great work, everyone!
(Deep exhale)
So, should we go?
I guess we should.
(Dog barking)
We were so close.
Staring at each other...
What if we had actually
been alone then...?
Hm...
Ah!
Whoa! Hey, are you okay?
Uh... Yeah, I'm all right.
Did you sprain yourself?
No, it's really not that bad.
Looks like the heel came off.
All right. I guess
I'll just take the
other one off, too.
There. That's much better.
Oww!
Hey, take it easy.
It isn't your fault
you had to wear shoes
you weren't used to.
Here.
Huh?
Umm... Thank you.
Hey, it's no big deal.
After all, protection
is part of my job.
(Gasp)
Man, a lot happened today,
didn't it? Uh...?
She's out for the count.
[HOUKI]
Ichika... like you...
Huh?
Completely hopeless.
(Flicking locket)
[Squall]
M, I'm coming in.
You initiated an
unauthorized contact.
Would you care to explain,
Madoka Orimura?
Your assigned task is
the seizing of other
nation's IS units...
However, if you recklessly
choose to indulge in
other endeavors...
(Evil laugh)
You always had good reflexes.
Hm...
Whether you're Madoka Orimura
or not, is irrelevant to
this mission...
For right now, you're simply
"M" of Phantom Task.
Until I settle the score,
that's my intention
Ah yes, the score...
with Ichika Orimura?
Hmph...!
He's no threat at all...
I can kill him
anytime I like.
Oh yes, right.
You're talking about the
score with Chifuyu Orimura?
Heh!
I wouldn't worry about her.
Since she no longer
has her own IS,
she could possibly pose
much of a challenge to you‐
Shut your mouth!
You don't even hold a candle
to someone of her talent!
Sigh...
Some of us need our sleep,
so I guess it's time
to take my leave.
As for you, lie low until
your next assignment.
As you wish.
I do like obedient girls.
[ICHIKA]
Who's there?!
And my name is...
Madoka Orimura.
[ICHIKA]
Uh...!
Hey, Chifuyu...
I keep telling you,
it's "Miss Orimura" here.
I know, but this is
about our family...
Do you think there might be
more than just you and me?
Like... another sister?
You're my only family...
It's just us.
[YAMADA]
The entire academy is
going to be participating
in a tag‐team tournament
designed to improve the skills
of pilots with
personal IS units.
A tag‐team, huh?
A number of IS units
from several countries'
have been hijacked.
And as you know, one of ours
was targeted during the
recent cultural festival.
(Sigh...)
Therefore, those of you
with personal units
are obliged to improve
your skill level.
Dismissed!
(School bell)
[CHARL]
Uh, Ichika, I made too much
food for my lunch today.
So would you like
to have some?
Wow, are you sure, Charl?
Oui! But of course!
Here, Bon Appétit, Ichika.
Oh! Thank you.
Mmm...! It's delicious!
Ya know, I think you've gotten
to be really good at making
Japanese food.
Really?
Merci beaucoup, Ichika.
Hey, this one
tastes good, too.
The batter's
nice and crispy.
[RININ]
Ah‐ha, there you are, Ichika.
Here! Please try some of my
Chinese stir‐fried pepper steak.
[ICHIKA]
Whoa, it looks super yummy!
[RININ]
Hehe... Doesn't it?
Wow! That is awesome!
(Giggle)
Hmph!
You two will be
great wives someday.
You're both such good cooks!
(Gasp)
Oh!
Here, Ichika, please have
a taste of my omelet now.
Here, have some
tea, too!
Wait a minute, why is it you're
both being so nice to me today?
Well, that is because...
Hey, we're always
nice to you, right?
[ICHIKA]
Uh... You are?
Um, Ichika, tell me...
When you're fighting,
which kind of partner...
Would you normally prefer
to fight alongside?
Hmm... Lemme see...
I still need to brush up
on my sniping skills...
so it'd be nice if my partner
could cover me there.
Mm‐hm!
But in the end I guess it's
all about working in harmony..
and just being
really compatible.
Compatible?
Well, what do you want?
Ah, well... I think...
that my ideal partner would be
someone who'd help me out
when I get cornered.
Someone, who'd be willing
to put everything
on the line for me.
Oh...
Oui, I agree with her.
I like those same qualities.
Oh, and also, I want that person
to be responsive to my needs.
Ah... Well everyone has
their type, I guess.
(Slurp)
Oh, man. Today's training
sure kicked my... ahh...
(Sigh)
Huh?!
Um... Ichika...
I want you to take care
of my sister for me!
Your what?
So. Anyway, here she is.
Her name is Kanzashi Sarashiki.
Huh...
[TATENASHI]
The thing is, she's kind of,
ya'know, the quiet type.
Oh...
However, she's really
quite skilled.
A representative contender
of Japan actually.
And yet...
And yet?
She doesn't have
her personal IS...
and it's kind of
because of you.
What?
Kanzashi's IS was created by
the same team of developers
who built yours.
The whole staff was directed
to work on the Byakushiki
while her unit got
put on the back burner.
Aw, man... I'm sorry.
That's why I want you
to pair up with her
and be Kanzashi's partner
in the upcoming
tag‐team tournament.
Pretty please!
Aw geez, Tatenashi, you
don't have to do the sad
puppy dog thing, ya'know.
Really? So does that
mean you'll do it?
Well yeah, I guess it does...
So, I suppose you
want me to go and talk
to Kanzashi in person now?
Mm‐hm. But please don't
mention my name to her.
Huh? But why not?
It's a little bit... um...
Let me guess...
You're not that close
to your sister, right?
Mm...
Understood. I'll approach her
as covertly as possible.
Oh, excellent.
I have been waiting for you.
I assume you will pair up with
me for the tag‐team tournament.
Well, actually, I...
This is a tournament entry form.
You will put your
signature on it now.
Ah, sorry, Laura,
but I've already decided
who I'm teaming up with.
Ach, nein!
You are my bride,
yet you will team up
with someone else?!
This response is
totally unacceptable!
Ah!
The only time I want to
smell burning flesh is
at a Korean Barbecue!
This matter is just between
me and my bride.
I've had it to here
with this "married" crap.
And besides, why would anyone
want an idiot with no manners
as thier sister‐in‐law.
Ah...
My mentor hates me.
Right, Orimura, would you
take Bodewig back to
her desk, please.
Class has been
delayed long enough.
Right.
[HOUKI]
You're too slow, Ichika!
I'm over here!
HYAAAAAAAAAH!
AHH!
You're finished!
I'm not finished yet!
(Houki humming)
I beat Ichika again today.
I said he was going to pick me
as his tag‐team partner.
And today clearly made me
the best choice.
So, if he asks nice,
I guess I'd consider it...
(Cecilia humming)
Ichika said he'd already
decided who he was
going to pair up with.
So he must've meant me, right?
Finally! Finally, I will
get to be with Ichika!
(Giddy sounds)
[HOUKI]
Hmm... looks like our
British contender is in
a good mood today.
Oh, hi, Houki.
So, how's it going?
Not too bad. And how are
you doing, Ms. Shinonono?
Oh, I'm awesome.
[HOUKI THOUGHT]
Hmph! That Cecilia...
I can't wait to see
the look on her face
when she hears that Ichika
is teaming up with me.
Well, I'm very pleased
to hear that.
[CECILIA THOUGHT]
Poor dear sweet Houki...
She has no idea that Ichika
is going to pick ME!
[HOUKI]
Well, see ya later, Cecilia.
[CECILIA]
Have a splendid day!
[BOTH THOUGHT]
And she takes the prize!
[GIRL]
Hey, that's Orimura
from Class One.
[OTHER GIRL]
Are you coming to see
someone in Class Four?
Is, uh...
Sarashiki here?
[Students]
Huh?
[GIRL]
Aww...
[ICHIKA]
Um, hi...
Nice to meet you.
My name's Ichika Orimura.
I know that.
You do?
What did you want?
Oh yeah, about that.
I want you to be my
partner for the upcoming
tag‐team tournament.
I don't think so.
Aw, don't say that.
Please. Uh‐
In all honesty...
I'm in my rights
to punch you now,
but then, it's just not
worth the effort.
[TATENASHI]
Hi there! Good morning,
all you sleepyheads!
Today it's going to be sunny,
then cloudy, with periods
of rain.
So, don't forget to have your
umbrella and rubbers handy!
Be safe, be prepard,
and everybody have a
really super day now! Mwah!
Oh, my, if it isn't
Miss Orimura...
Is something wrong?
[CHIFUYU]
Next time on Infinite Stratos 2,
"Open Your Heart".