Who's there?!
And my name is...
Madoka Orimura.
I must take your life!
Grr! Gahh!
Hmph. I wonder how
long this'll last.
(gasps)
Laura! ,/
Damn you...!
You have a lot of nerve,
going after my bride like that!
Hyah!
(gasps)
Laura:
Silent Zephyrus?!
(gasps)
What a pain. Huh?
She got away?
(sighs)
Are you okay, Laura?
That is what I should
be asking you.
Since it was you who she was
after... but for what reason?
I don't know...
Huh?
What's wrong?
Hmm... Laura, your eye
is really pretty.
Huh?!
Ichika:
It's kinda like
a gemstone.
Ach du lieber! This is
no time for that!
You just
got attacked!
Well, I don't usually
get to see it.
Pretty...
Ichika said that
I look... pretty!
And of course, your timing
couldn't have been better!
Well, that is because...
I was looking for a
chance where I could
be alone with you.
(gasps) I cannot believe
you made me say that!
WAAUUGH!
(panting)
Ichika:
What was that for?
(siren sounds)
Ichika:
So we're supposed to be
escorting IS equipment?
Oui.
Recently, several countries
have asked us to test their
prototype equipment.
But then...
Sorry, but I've got
urgent family business.
You see, there's a
VERY important meeting
that I must attend.
Actually I already have a
different duty assignment.
Ja, Clarissa,
you were saying...
Everyone
seems busy...
I guess I will
do it alone.
Hm?
Huh?
You did not have
to come with me, Ichika...
You were just
ambushed the other day.
But that doesn't mean
I should stand by
and let you take all of
this on by yourself.
Ichika:
Don't worry,
it'll be fine.
(sighs)
Ichika:
Huh?
Or... it
won't be fine.
I'll check it out!
Ichika, wait!
Who're those guys?
There's no nationality
or ID code!
Let's go, Charl!
Right, Ichika!
Hm? Huh?!
Damn it! They're way
too fast to hit!
If you surrender now,
no one will get hurt...
is it a deal, ladies?
They're IS pilots!
Who the hell cares?
Waste 'em!
(yelps)
HAAAAH!
HYAAAH!
Dammit!
(high‐pitched battle cry)
Not too bad!
Oh, no! You can't
escape!
HAAAAA!
HIYAAAAA!
Your poor handling
is making my Revive weep!
SHUT UP!
HYAAAAAHHH!
(pained scream)
Ichika!
HYAH!
Just give up!
You have no chance
against us.
(sighs)
(struggling)
CHARL!
Oh, Ichika, dearest!
Are you feeling alright today?
Yeah, sure, why?
Could you be
any slower?
You should never let your
guard down, Ichika.
Sorry. I just didn't
want you to worry.
Rinin:
(sighs) Honestly.
You're hopeless.
Cecilia:
Oh! He certainly is!
Ichika:
I said I'm
sorry, Jeez!
Hm...
Orimura appears to
have no physiological
impairments at all...
And yet...
Yamada:
I detect an anomaly with the
Byakushiki's quantum conversion.
Orimura?
Ichika:
Yes, Ma'am.
Yukihira, engage.
Huh?
He's not able to deploy
his weaponry, Ma'am.
And why's that?
I can't say without
conducting further tests.
Hm...
Alright.
Hand over your IS.
Huh...?
Hold on...
What if Phantom Task returns
and I don't have anything
to help defend us with?
But that's just it.
You'd be in worse trouble
if your Byakushiki
failed unexpectedly.
Yeah, but...
It's better to be
powerless than defective.
Of could it be...?
That you're just scared
to be without your IS?
U‐uh... Hm...
No, I'm not
scared, Chifuyu.
Mm... Good boy.
Next question...
How're we going to handle it
if the girls find out
about this situation?
It'll probably
cause an uproar...
However, viewing this
from a security perspective,
I believe it's essential
for us to notify
all the representative
contenders.
Oh swell, this is going
to be a double headache.
No... please do not
let them know.
It is my duty to protect him!
I must... I must
protect Ichika...
Ichika, tell me
which one you like?
Ichika:
Gah!
What is this?!
Hey, Laura!
What are you doing, showing
him that kind of stuff?!
Ichika! Close
your virgin eyes!
I am merely trying
to determine
what my bride's
tastes are.
"Your bride's tastes"?
Ja... Clarissa
told me...
When a young girl
is in love,
A certain type of
incident may happen...
This is called,
the "panty flash event."
In this... the boy finds
a glimpse of her panties.
So you MUST wear panties you
want Ichika to see at all times!
Ohh!
Und these..
horizontal‐striped panties...
Laura:
are supposedly the very best
kind to boost your likability!
The striped panties...
are the best?
Well, uh, this design
isn't bad at all.
Yeah, I agree...
I have some myself.
Chelsea, I want to order
some new knickers.
And it's imperative that
they have horizontal stripes...
No, no, no!
You've got
this all wrong!
Perhaps Ichika is flustered
because it was the truth...?
Obviously, I have
a very modest bride.
(laughs)
THAT'S NOT RIGHT EITEHR!
Und which kind of
underwear do you like?
Laura, you are not supposed
to talk about things like that
in front of
a boy. Huh?
(gasps)
Uh, excuse moi!
Oh...!
Hm?
Oh... Sacre bleu!
Ahh! What has happened
to my underwear?!
(gasps)
I detect an anomaly
with the Byakushiki's
quantum conversion.
Yamada:
He's seems unable
to deploy his weaponry.
Oh...
Could it be... that
the same thing is happening
now with my underwear?!
(whimpers)
Fortunately,
I have a spare!
Mon dieu! Not again!
What should I do?
(door knocks)
Ah!
Hey Charl,
are you in there?
Gasp! Ichika!
What is the
matter?
Well, class has
started already!
Huh?! Oh, right! Sorry!
I'm sorry,
Ichika.
Is something wrong?
Well, sort of, but um...
It's okay now.
All right...
let's go then.
Wait, Ichika! Give me a second.
Slow down! Slow down!
Come ON! The bell already rang!
And you know how my sister is!
Oui... I know
this, but...
Ichika:
(growls) FASTER!
We gotta hurry!
Whoa...! Do not
pull me like that!
Wha! You okay?!
Uh... I.. am
all right! Ah!
Hm?
(progressively higher
pitched screams)
NOOOOOOOO!!!
(pained yell, groan)
Sacrebleu! How long
can this keep going on?
Ah, Houki.
Uh‐huh?
May I sit here?
Sure. Go ahead.
Oh!
Is something
wrong?
Oh! It is nothing...
Ooh... this seat
is very cold!
Over here!
Okay, Charlotte!
Got it! Attack mode!
Charl:
Huh?
Uh, my timing was off.
(nervously laughs)
Why on Earth did they have
to ask me to help out
with this sort of thing,
today of all days?
Hey Charl!
You need a hand?
Hm? Eek! AAH!
WAAHH!
(gasps)
Come on, Charl, there
must be something going
on with you today.
I'm so sorry...
Ichika:
(sighs)I know.
The issues
with Byakushiki
must have gotten you worried.
It's my fault, right?
Oh, it is not
like that at all.
Actually I am very glad
to be of help to you, Ichika.
Well, that's fine, but I don't
want you to have a breakdown.
Just be careful.
Mm‐hm.
You are so sweet, Ichika.
Huh? What? Did you
say something?
Nothing!
(giggles)
Hm?
Laura:
Oh... ah...!
(horrified gasps)
Hallo, Clarissa. Laura...
This is an emergency!
What?! Charlotte Dunois
has no underwear?!
Oh!
It seems as though I
may have accidentally
opened up
Pandora's box here...
Bodewig.
Do you remember the "panty flash
event" we discussed?
Laura:
Of course I do.
Sometimes... in some situations
you cannot see the panties
which are supposed
to be there.
Laura:
What did you say?!
You see, this case,
codename: "The Full
Commando Sneak Attack",
Can be a trick of light!
Or perhaps, a cheat
of the viewing angle!
Oh, I see...!
That means..
Charlotte was...
Clarissa:
In all probability, you simply
were not able to see them.
Laura:
I see...
So Charlotte actually
was wearing the panties.
That is good.
Ja, that is very good. ,/
I expect nothing less
from our Squad's XO!
I agree!
She doesn't love Japanese anime
and manga for nothing!
I admire her and
want to be like her!
Laura:
Then it seems I will not have
to lose a comrade over this. ,/
She is your "comrade"...?
Hmph! Hearing you refer
to someone else that way
makes your commander jealous.
Laura:
Huh? What was that?
Oh, it was nothing.
Leader, we of the
Black Hare Squadron,
will always be on your side...
Please do not ever forget that.
Laura:
I appreciate that, Clarissa.
Thank you for helping me out
with this, Ichika...
I will go tell the teacher,
so you can go ahead
and return to the
classroom.
Okay... Don't push
yourself too heard.
(sighs)
Thank God he
did not find out.
Whatever went wrong
with Byakushiki
has now happened to
my underwear...!
(sighs) I must do
something about it soon.
But that means I will
need to have Revive
inspected, as well...
And as long as that is
the case, I will not
be able to protect Ichika.
Aside from that,
what will happen if Ichika
should discover that I do not
have any
underwear on...?
I'm shocked to find out
you're into things like that...
Even more than when I found
out you were a girl.
But it's not...
like that!
Truthfully, I'm stunned...
You going commando...
Please, Ichika...!
I can explain!
I'm disappointed in
you, Charl. Good‐bye...
No, Ichika!
Please WAIT!
That could happen...
Mon dieu, it really could!
Anyway, I will have to keep
my problem a secret
until Ichika's Byakushiki
has returned to normal.
What?!
Huh...? Ah, bonjour. What a
coincidence seeing you here.
I was just moving
some materials to the
reference room for a teacher.
Well, bye‐bye!
Uh!
Not so fast,
Charlotte.
Exactly what you were
talking about...?
Why don't you tell us
about it in greater detail.
(nervous laugh)
Houki:
Why didn't you tell
us about that sooner?!
Cecilia:
You shouldn't have hesitated!
Don't you realize that
you're being targeted?
Uh... I guess you guys figured
out about Byakushiki, huh?
Mmm‐hm!
Then I have no choice
but to give you my
full‐time protection.
Oh, no. This situation
definitely calls
for me and Blue Tears
to step in.
Are you kidding?!
There's no way a
long‐distance sniper
could ever be his bodyguard!
Just leave it up to me
and my Shenlong.
Cecilia:
What did you say?
Rinin:
What's your deal?!
Actually...
Houki:
Hey, calm down!
Here. This way!
Sorry, Ichika.
But it wasn't your fault
that it happened!
I know, but...
Get down!
ARE YOU INSANE?!
Oh, there's no need to worry,
as I decreased the output.
And now you shall be taken under
Cecilia's protective wing.
Don't shoot at the guy
you're protecting!
Look out!
GAAH...!
AH! Now Rin's
gone psycho!
Don't worry...
I just tapped it.
YOU TAPPED IT
EIGHT‐INCHES DEEP!
I've got you covered!
Aaaaahhhh!!
No, I'll do it!
I'm the one who's going
to protect Ichika!
Oh no, not on
my watch, you wont!
(growls)
I'll make it clear to
everyone to see who Ichika's
true childhood friend is!
Uh, all right...
calm down.
Tatenashi:
That's quite enough!
There will be no more
using your IS
for private purposes
on school grounds.
(giggles)
No one invited the
student council
This is a personal issue
we're dealing with!
You're not part of it,
so butt out!
I see. I see.
Well, maybe I ought to just go
ahead and join in the fun...
And then after I
defeat all of you,
I'll get to have
Ichika, okay?
I like how obedient
you girls are...
Now I want the three of
you to rake all the sand
on the school grounds.
Huh?!
Now, what kind of example would
I set if I didn't penalize you
after making such a commotion?
Well, I'll leave you to it!
(sighs)
(sighs) I feel kinda
guilty, now. ,/
Mm‐hm...
Oh, well. I guess
I gotta go.
Huh? Go where?
To go get yelled
at by Chifuyu. ,/
It's not your fault. This
wouldn't have happened if it
weren't for Byakushiki.
Then I... should
go with you, no?
But you've already done
the best you could, Charl. ,/
Let me do some of
the hard work for a change.
But I...
And thanks for
everything today...
you've been great.
Ohh...
Ichika is leaving now,
and it is because of me...
Ichika did not do
anything wrong...
Does this mean that I should
have told him the truth earlier?
That is impossible!
I will not be able to protect
Ichika if I tell him that,
and he is going
to hate me!
But then...
what am I
supposed to do?
Charl's Mother:
Why did you not
tell me about it?
Because I thought
you would get mad.
Oh...
Are you
hurt, ma chère?
You are not mad?
What for?
Because I broke your
favorite mirror, mama.
There is nothing that is more
important to me than you...
Charlotte.
Mama... I am sorry!
I am proud of you because you
said you were sorry.
But can you promise me
that you are going to
be honest from now on?
I promise will not
tell a lie again, Mama!
That is right...
Ichika is not going to hate
me because of this...
As long as I am
honest with him...
Everything will be alright!
Charl:
Ichika, wait!
Huh?
There is something important
that I need to tell you.
Uh... tell me?
About... what?
I just... wanted to...
What do you
think you're doing?!
I'm getting to it!
To what?!
I want... to show you my...
secret!
Charlotte.
HUH?!
AHH!
What... What on Earth
was I doing just now?
Bonjour! So, what is up?
(gasps)
Hm... Oh! So you
DO wear underwear.
Of course I do...!
I do...? Huh...?
Yes, I do!
Look, Ichika! Look at this!
You big pervert.
Ichika:
ARE YOU KIDDING ME?!
Chifuyu:
Have you determined
the cause yet?
It seems one of the
prototype units that was
scheduled to be brought in
had an option that would
execute quantum conversion
more effectively.
It must be the one that was
destroyed in the attack.
Right, and when it went out
of control it apparently had
some kind of impact
on Byakushiki.
Luckily, the effect
was temporary,
and it now appears
to be back to normal.
Hmm...
Either way, the whole thing
was suspiciously inconvenient.
I'm just glad that
Orimura's okay now.
Well, given that his
carelessness caused this,
I'd say he got...
what he deserved.
Uh? What now?
Nothing. Really.
Yeah right, so what else
have you learned?
Yamada:
They had no ties
to Phantom Task.
They were just
industrial spies.
Hmph.
(sighs)
So, the quantum conversion
only affected your underwear?
Oui! It was worse
than commando training!
What I believe you should have
done is to put on something
that would not be
recognized as panties,
such as these... bloomers!
Ah...!
Bloomers?
Why did I not
think of that?
You know, a French
queen once said...
"If they have no panties,
then let them wear
bloomers instead." Ja.
She did not say that!
(groan)
Laura:
It is a time of great unrest.
We are engaged in the
great civil war over Ichika.
We of the Black Hare
Squadron may occupy very
little territory, and yet...
our spirits continue to
soar higher than even
the great Mount Fuji!
Und now, we depart for war!
Ach du lieber! Frau Orimura?!
Chifuyu:
Stand aside, Bodwig.
Next time on Infinite Stratos 2,
"Sisters".