(giggle) The goddess
of victory has truly
smiled upon me this day.
Nien! The last laugh
will be belonging to me.
Grah! D'oh!
[Houki, thinking]
I'm gonna be in the same
group as Ichika today,
I can't afford to
waste this chance.
[Houki]
Buddha, help me!
(laughing boastfully)
D'aaaahhhh!
(defeated)
[Charl]
Oh, is that your camera?
Yeah...
I brought it from home so
I could take some pictures
during the trip.
For class mementoes.
"Class mementoes"?
Yeah, since I'm the class
representative,
I'll be separated
from the group.
I'll be wandering around taking
photos of the scenery.
Separated from the group?
You mean you will not be
joining the rest of us?
How could you neglect to
tell us such an important
thing? How could you?!
What is this?
Why are you so mad?
(Houki, Laura, Charl &
Cecilia arguing with Ichika)
(chuckle) I hope this is going
to be a great trip.
Hmmm...
Yeah, sure...
Wow!
[Charl]
Ohh... what a lovely garden!
[Houki]
Yeah, the hotel
has great scenery.
[Aikawa]
Everyone, come on!
Hurry up! This way!
[Charl & Houki] Oh?
[Ichika] Huh? Guh?!
(Students screaming excitedly)
[Aikawa]
This is great! (laughing)
[Takatsuki]
I wonder what the
rooms look like.
[Nohohon]
Yay, yay, yay!
[Ichika]
Unnghh... so beautiful...
[Yamada]
Everyone, listen up!
All of you are going to be on
free‐time in your groups after
this meeting is concluded.
We're all scheduled to pay
a visit to Kiyomizu‐dera
Temple this evening.
Make sure that you arrive...
no later than the scheduled
time... Understood...?
You're dismissed!
[Students]
Yes, ma'am!
(Ichika worn out)
[Yamada] Um...
[Ichika] Hm?
A piece of luggage was
just delivered for you.
Huh?
Mm‐hm...?
Is something wrong?
This piece of luggage was
delivered for me, but I
don't know what it is.
Hm...?
[Ichika] Uwahh... What the‐
Kanzashi] Whoa!
Ta‐da...!
It's me, Miss Tatenashi!
T‐Tatenashi?!
Sister?! You!
[Kanzashi] (growling angrily)
[Tatenashi] Ahh! Kanzashi,
[Tatenashi] please stop that!
Hey, hey! Cut it out!
[Ichika] Uhh...
[Kanzashi] (struggling)
[Tatenashi] Little sister! I
haven't done anything yet! Wah!
[Kanzashi]
Give me a hand, Ichika!
[Ichika]
Uh, right!
[Kanzashi] Uwaugh!
[BOTH] Ungha! (exhale)
[Kanzashi]
Whew...!
[Ichika]
Man, what was that?
(chuckling)
[Cecilia]
Fleeting feelings...
dancing in the autumn breeze...
[Cecilia]
Oh, yes...
The season of love
has definitely arrived.
[Ichika]
Hey, Cecilia! Do you mind?
Huh?
(exhaling)
Absolutely beautiful.
[Cecilia]
(happy) Huh?!
[Cecilia, thinking]
My, he's such an impatient boy.
If he wants to take photographs
of me, he should simply reveal
his intentions.
[Cecilia]
Did it come out beautifully?
I'd like to have a look at
it, if you wouldn't mind.
Of course.
Uwah!
[Ichika]
Aren't the autumn maple
leaves beautiful?
Look at the foliage!
Ichika..! What on earth
is this supposed to be?!
Huh...? It didn't come out
blurry or something, did it?
[Cecilia]
That is not the point here!
In the first place, you are
so totally‐
[Nohohon] Orimu! Orimu!
[Cecilia] Uh?
[Nohohon]
Will you take our picture?
Oh! Yeah!
(grinning)
Huh?
Over here, Orimura!
Hey, no fair..!
Over here, too!
Uh...! Okay...!
Please wait for your turn.
(seething)
[Tanimoto]
Okay... make sure you get
everything in the shot!
[Aikawa]
Hold on! Let me get
in the photo, too!
[Kishihara]
It really is gold!
[Nohohon]
Whoa... look at all the koi!
[Kagami]
Check it out, you guys!
See the bride?
[Takatsuki]
Ohhhh... The all‐white
kimono is divine!
Ah... Ichika!
(Ichika struggling)
Huh...? Yeah?
Uh... What are
you doing?
[Ichika]
Ah... My lens cap fell
underneath this.
(pondering)
I see... I think my hand
will fit... Shall I try?
Oh, thanks.
[Charl]
Now then...
Hm... It is too
dark to see very well...
[Ichika]
Oh... I guess you
can't reach it, huh?
(giggle) No problem
at all, Ichika.
[Ichika] Is it there?
[Charl] Ungh! I'm trying.
[Ichika] Are you close?
[Charl] It's too big!
[Ichika] Huh? Uh, Charl... Um...
[Charl] It doesn't fit!
[Ichika] I see something...
[Charl] Huh...? But I still
cannot see it.
That... isn't what I'm seeing!
[Charl, straining] I got it!
[Ichika whimpering]
[Charl] Here you go.
Uh, thank you...
But I, uh...
Is something wrong?
It... kinda...
[Ichika]
...went up.
Huh? (gasp) OHH!
And I'm sorry.
Well... I will forgive you,
[Charl]
if you will spend a little
time with me after this. Okay?
[Ichika]
Uh, okay.
(Crowd chattering)
[Rinin]
It's not like me to ask
a favor of the gods,
but since this shrine is so
famous for making successful
relationships,
my prayers might
be answered, right?
(giggle)
[Rinin, thinking]
Please... will you make that
idiot notice how I feel about
him? Even just a little.
[Rinin] Right!
[Rinin & Cecilia ] Uwuh?!
(awkward laughing)
[Rinin]
What a coincidence..!
So, uh, is this shrine
famous for something?
Uh, I just happened
to be in this area,
so I decided I'd stop
by and check it out.
[Cecilia]
Oh! I just happened to be in
this area as well,
so I decided to pay a visit,
too... So here we both are...
What a delightful coincidence,
huh?
[Rinin] Yeah, isn't it?
(nervous laughter)
[Rinin & Cecilia] Hmph. Hm?
(splashing)
I wish to be blessed
with many children.
Laura...! When did‐
Hold a second!
What did you just say?
[Laura]
Excuse me?
Is this not the place where
these wishes are granted?
[Rinin & Cecilia] (sigh)
[Charl]
Uh, bonjour!
[All]
Hm?
Yo!
[Rinin & Cecilia] Ichika?!
(angry reaction)
[Charl]
(embarrassed)
[Cecilia]
Uhh..! Look..!
We demand to know
what is going on!
That's right! Have you two
been on a secret date?!
Oh, no. It is
not like that.
Yeah, really. No way
that would happen!
[Charl] (aghast)
[Ichika] Anyway, the
magazines in the lobby say
getting angry and frowning gives
you girls wrinkles and stuff.
[Rinin & Cecilia] (seething)
So since we're all here on
vacation... let's have fun!
[Ichika] Huh?
[Girls] (fuming))
[Ichika]
Uh‐uh! (sweating)
Jeez! What the hell did
I say or do this time?!
[Girls]
Ichika!
[Yamada]
Um, excuse me, Miss Orimura...
But is there something that's
bothering you?
[Chifuyu]
Of course there is.
Our school and our students
have already been the targets
of several attacks.
We need to keep a close eye
on everything, and ensure
that our students actually
enjoy their trip.
[Yamada]
(happy) Yes, ma'am!
[Ichika]
Whew! I finally
managed to lose them.
[Nohohon, singing]
Hey there! Orimu!
[Ichika] Huh?
[Nohohon] (happy giggles)
[Ichika]
Uh? Nohohon?
[Nohohon, singing]
I'm being chased by Kan‐chan!
[Kanzashi]
Honne, please wait! Oh, where
are you going?! (panting)
[Ichika]
Uh? Kanzashi... what's
up with the outfit?
[Kanzashi]
Ah! Ichika!
[Ichika] Hm?
Um... It wasn't my idea...
I only got it... because
everybody else said I should
try wearing something fancy.
I really didn't want to do it,
but well, you know...
[Ichika]
Well, I think it looks
really great on you!
Um! You... think so?
[Ichika] Sure!
[Ichika]
Uh? (frightened sound)
[Laura] Target locked!
[Ichika & Kanzashi] Huh?!
[Charl]
What looks "great" on her...
Ichika Orimura?
Yeah, what she said!
Unforgivable!
Gah! Not again!
ICHIKA!
[Cecilia] You won't get away!
[Charl] You will pay!
[Rinin] Big time!
[Ichika] Whooooaa!
[Ichika]
Hold on Kanzashi!
We're outta here! Ahh!
[Kanzashi] (unsure)
(Ichika breathing heavily)
[Kanzashi]
Ichika...
[Kanzashi] Oh, no! Look out!
[Ichika] WAAAAAHH!!
Uh.. What happened..?
Hey! What's going on!?
[Ichika] Un‐uh... Oh crap!
[Houki] (seethe) Why
you little...!
What in the hell do
you think you're doing?!
[Ichika] Huuh?!
[Cecilia]
Oh? Mmmmm!
This is delicious...! Thank you
so much for treating me, Ichika!
[Ichika]
Yeah, how did that happen again?
[Rinin]
What was that? Got a problem?
[Ichika]
Uh...
[Rinin]
You're lucky that we're letting
you off the hook this easily.
[Ichika]
(sigh) Ah‐huh...
It's a good thing that Houki
knew about such a great place
for a picnic.
[Houki]
Uh! Yeah... I guess it was...
(sigh)
[Houki, thinking]
Except that, I found this place
so that Ichika and I could come
here by ourselves...
[Kanzashi]
Chomp! (chewing)
Hey! This is good!
(giggle)
(sigh)
(Laura intrigued)
[Ichika] Hm? What is it??
Uhh... What are these things?
Oh, those are
Japanese sweets, Laura.
Mmhm, would you like to try one?
[Laura]
Uh! (hesitant)
[Bunny A]
Have mercy on us!
[Bunny B]
We exist so that
we may be eaten.
And that is why there is
delicious sweet bean paste
inside our tummies!
[Bunny A]
(sobbing) But I don't...
[Bunny B]
All right, then. You may go
ahead and eat me first. Bon
appetite!
(hesitant)
Just try one.
They're great!
[Laura] Uhhh...
(determined)
(chomp)
[Laura]
(gasp) So tasty...
[Ichika]
Mm‐hm, Told ya!
[Ichika, thinking]
What did she say, I should
never forget those who were
in my past.
(thoughtful)
[Houki]
Hey, um... Ichika!
[Ichika]
Oh... Houki!
Why aren't you
with the others?
Oh well... it looks like
we've gotten separated.
You know...
there's supposed to be
a wonderful bamboo forest
close by.
Have you been there already?
No, not yet... But it sounds
great... You wanna go?
Aah... Yeah, let's go!
[Houki]
(sigh) This is such
a lovely place...
[Ichika]
Mm‐hm.
Hmph, it really is.
[Houki]
I was really hoping that I
would get to come here...
...together, with you.
[Ichika]
Hey... Do you remember how you
and I used to take walks
together like this?
[Houki]
Uh...? Yeah, I remember that...
You'd ask me to go for
walks with you after we
finished training...
Sweet memories.
[Houki]
Hey, uh... Is there something
wrong?
You don't sound like yourself.
[Ichika]
What? You think so, huh?
Oh by the way, can I get a shot?
[Squall] Or would you prefer...
that I take it for you?
[Houki & Ichika] Huh?
You'd rather be in the photo
together, wouldn't you?
[Ichika]
Oh, sure. We appreciate it.
(happy) Thank you
so much, ma'am!
I did have great‐looking
subjects... Both of you.
Oh, thanks.
Enjoy the rest of your
trip... Ichika Orimura, kay?
Did I... tell her my name?
Un‐uh...
[Yamada]
The veranda outside the
Kiyomizu‐dera Temple's main hall
sits thirteen meters
atop the hillside.
It is supported by a "hell
stop" structure comprised
of 139 wooden pillars.
(Students intrigued)
C'est magnifique!
It's quite beautiful!
Hey, everyone, make sure
that you return back to the
monorail platform at the
appointed time, okay?
[Students]
Yes, ma'am!
I'm going to check
out souvenirs.
Hey, do you want to go
see what's over there? (giggle)
Oh?
Hm...? Etiquette requires that
you ask for permission before
you take a lady's picture.
[Ichika]
Oh... well I...
(small chuckle) Be sure to
give me a copy later, okay?
Eh?
(sigh)
(giggle)
Hello, Ichika.
Hey, what's shakin', Charl?
I was hoping you could show
me the pictures you took.
[Ichika]
My pictures...? Okay.
Whoa...
You have been to so
many places today.
[Ichika]
Uh! Um, places?
I'd very much like to
have a look at them, too.
Huh? D'uoh
(whimpering)
Too close...
[Cecilia]
Have a look at this one.
It's really wonderful,
don't you think?
[Charl] But I am not done
looking at them yet.
[Cecilia] Well, neither am I.
[Charl] But I got here first!
[Ichika] Just take turns!
Orimura, I want
to see them, too.
It's not fair!
Me, too, Orimu! Me, too!
(Girls arguing)
[Ichika, smushed]
Come on, girls!
[Ichika]
You can't all look at
them at the same time!
I'm not done yet!
Give it to me!
[Ichika] Ack!
(Girls still arguing)
(Ichika getting pushed around)
[Ichika] AH!
[Ichika] Ohhh...! (Sigh)
[Students] Oh! Ah! No! Aw...
I guess, I'll go get it.
[Ichika]
(sigh) Let's see...
It should be around here.
Huh?
You again!
[Madoka]
Ichika Orimura... I am
here to take.. your life.
Geh!
[Madoka]
Come... Black Knight!
(wincing)
[Houki]
Hm? Uh... Hey, Cecilia!
(Cecilia gasps)
[Houki]
It's almost time for us to
meet up at the station, so
where are you going?
Oh, Ichika still hasn't come
back yet... so I thought I had
better go find out what's
keeping him.
Where could he be?
[Yamada]
Okay everyone, make sure
your travel buddy is
sitting next to you!
Uh, ma'am.. Orimura
isn't here yet!
And Shinonono and Alcott
haven't come back yet either.
Hm? Look at that.
[Girls] Huh?
(concerned)
Miss Yamada... Go ahead and
take these students back to the
hotel,
and I'll see you there
once I find the others.
[Yamada]
Hm? Yes, ma'am.
(gasp)
What the...!
Huh?
Hmmm...
[Tatenashi]
So here you are, gazing down
from the highest perspective.
I guess celebrities don't think
like the rest of us, huh?
Hmph.
[Squall]
"Moscow's Thick Fog",
I believe...
Wasn't that the name of your IS?
[Tatenashi]
That's what it used to be
called... But it's the
"Mysterious Lady" now.
[Squall]
(chuckling) I see.
[Tatenashi]
So, what's Phantom Task up
to...? Nothing good, I'll bet.
[Squall] My... Such attitude.
And just what do you know about
our plans in the first place,
Miss Sarashiki?
[Tatenashi]
I won't let you do
whatever you please.
(chuckle) The situation was
practically perfect... but I
guess you arrived just a little
too late!
HYAAAH!!
(screaming, struggling)
You see, we've already begun!
(struggling)
[Students] AAAAHH!!
What's happening?
I'm not sure...
I'll try to hack
into the control system.
Miss Orimura, what's going on?
We need to contact the
academy immediately
and tell them we need
military backup stat!
Understood, ma'am!
[Chifuyu, thinking]
So they're willing to
use any means, are they?
(panting)
Ichika!
(crying out)
(recovering)
[Houki] Huh!
[Cecilia] Oh?
(maniacal laughter)
[Autumn]
Sorry... I'm not going to allow
that, you little brats!
Who are you, you psycho?!
I'm Autumn, dammit. How
could you forget about me?!
Okay, "Madoka"...
why're you after me?
Heh... You're not
the one I'm after.
[Ichika]
Eh? What?
[Madoka]
My true objective is...
Chifuyu Orimura...
to kill her.
(gasp) Kill her?! My sister?
[Ichika] AAAAAAAHHHH!
[Ichika, voiceover]
So... this model kit is really
popular right now, huh?
All right then, I'm going
to try to make it.
Let's see... This is the
arm joint, right...?
Hm... Yeah, yeah...
Hey, this moves!
That's pretty cool!
No wonder Big Sister Chifuyu
is crazy about it...
(gasp) Chifuyu...!?
[Chifuyu, voiceover]
Next time on Infinite Stratos 2,
"Girls Over".