Hm...
Tatenashi:
Ichika!
Hm?
Ichika:
Hm?!
(giggles)
No way! AHHH!
Tatenashi:
Hey, Ichika...
is something wrong?
What do you mean
"is something wrong"...?!
You're what's wrong! Put some
clothes on for God's sake!
But... I did.
Uh! Pants! I was
thinking about pants!
It's stuck!
(power struggle)
Fine...!
Give it up!
I want to have one
of your massages...
Tatenashi:
Everyone says
you're so good at them!
It's so I can be relaxed for
tomorrow's school festival.
Come on... pretty please?
Ichika:
As a guy, it's NOT a good idea
for me to massage THAT body.
It's a terrible idea!
If you continue
to resist me,
I'm going to have
to do this by force.
I won't let you do that!
All right then...
If you won't open it,
then I'll just rip the door
off its hinges!
Aaah!
GAAAHHH!
Get‐them‐off!
(giggles)
Now... massage me!
Massage me!
Fine... if
you insist.
Bienvenue!
This way,
please... Milady
I don't believe it!
Orimura's actually going to
wait on us personally!
And he's even dressed
like a butler!
And you get to take
pictures with him, too!
Just the two of you!
Can you believe it?!
Hey, you butler over there!
Aren't you going to
take me to my table?
Huh?
Rin? When did
YOU get here?
Mmph! Never you mind!
It so happens that Class Two
is doing a Chinese café.
Ichika:
Hm?
Hang on... is that the way
you usually wear your hair?
Oh... this...?
Yeah. I put it up.
That's what
it is!
I knew there was
something different!
Ah... but
the thing is...
it's not all
that different.
I do this way
all the time...
Uh! Just take me
to my table already!
Of course...
if you'll follow me,
(gentlemanly)
this way, Madame.
(gasps)
What'd you call me?
(gentlemanly)
I'll take your order
whenever you're ready.
Hm... Let's see...
Oh!
Would you please
tell me about this
"Treat Your
Butler" Special?
Well Madam,
I think it would actually
be much better if you tried
our famous cake
special instead.
Hey, you were trying to trick me
just now, weren't you?
Hmph. Certainly not.
Well, in that case, I'd like
you to bring me one of these
"Treat Your Butler" Specials.
Your "Treat Your Butler"
Special... Madame.
Um, so...
I don't get it.
Why did you come sit down
at the table with me?
Uh, well, I suppose I don't
actually mind you being here.
But what kind of
"special" is this anyway?
You get to feed me now.
What?
Like I said...
you get to feed your butler.
That's what the "special" is.
And what kind of
stupid special is that...?
You mean the customer is
supposed to feed YOU sweets?
That's why I didn't
want you to pick it...
But you don't have to go through
with it if you don't want to.
That's really dumb...
But since you already
brought it out here...
I might as well...
Hmm...
Wait! You mean that I get
to feed you something?!
Okay then!
Now, say "aah...!"
Aaah...
I fed something sweet to you,
so now... it's your turn t‐
Gah!
I'm so sorry...
But I'm afraid that
service is not part
of our special, Madam.
Hmph!
Mmm...
(sighs)
Rin...
Hm?
Nothing... It's just
that you're kind of cute.
(choking)
Hey, do you need
a Heimlich or something?
What in the heck
is your problem today?!
I was... just talking
about the way you eat.
You think... that
the way I eat is "cute"?
Yeah... Just like
a squirrel.
WAAAUGHH!! ,/
Hmph!
What's HER deal?
Huh?
Do you have a minute?
Sure...
Okay... So you're
Reiko... Makigami?
Yes... I'm so excited to be
meeting with you today...
we'd like to interest
you in equipping your IS
with our
company's products.
Well, I'm not totally sure when
it comes to things like that...
Come on. Don't
be like that.
Just have a look at
our supplemental armor
or these secondary
thrusters.
And if you act right now,
we're even going to throw in
leg blades as well.
Uh... but I really
don't need any...
Excuse me, ma'am,
I'm sorry to interrupt...
but the next customer
is waiting for him.
(scoffs)
Ichika:
Uh... please excuse me.
I have to go now.
(sighs)
You're a real lifesaver...
Thanks, Takatsuki..
A lot of people have
been trying to recommend
different equipment
for the Byakushiki lately. ,/
Don't worry
about it...
I guess you have a
lot on your plate.
Mm...
you can go ahead and take
a break now, if you like.
Why don't you go look at the
other class projects?
Huh? Now?
Sure! I guess you can have
about thirty minutes, alright?
Well, okay then, if you
think it'd be all right.
Oh, it's perfectly alright...
I'll gladly accompany you.
Oh! That's not fair, Cecilia!
No kidding! In that case,
I'm going, too!
Right! Let's go, Ichika.
Wait just a minute!
You know you can't all go
and leave the café unattended!
Rock‐paper‐scissors
for it.
One!
Two!
Trois!
Do it!
Oh‐ho‐ho‐ho‐ho!
(French horn blares)
Whoa! I totally
blew it!
Oh, no, you're a
natural with those lips.
But our club offers
private tutoring.
No, I don't think
it's for me...
But maybe Cecilia
would like to.
Do you think
I could...?
I've never played any sort
of wind instrument before.
Seriously...?
I'd have thought you'd
already play the flute
or something like that...
because you're a well‐bred
and elegant, ya know?
Well‐bred and elegant? ,/
Oh‐ho‐ho‐ho!
Come on. Give it
a blow, it's easy!
But...
that's the same one
that you just...
Huh?
It would be an
indirect... kiss
Huh? What'd you say?
Oh, it's nothing really...
Please don't worry about it.
At... long last...
here I go.
Music Club Captain:
Wait a second.
Let me change the
mouthpiece first.
Uh!
(sobbing)
Look at the time, I'd better
get back to work, now.
Ta‐da!
Aaack! Uh...
Tatenashi?!
(giggles)
Hello, Ichika...
I'm here because we have decided
that you will help us out
with the student council's
interactive play.
Huh?
Just come with me...
it's right this way.
Huh?
Tatenashi:
Don't struggle!
What a good boy!
Hold on, wait!
Tatenashi:
Here. Go change into this
and then come to the stage.
Huh?
And don't forget this...
it's vital.
Consider yourself...
crowned!
Yeah, but...
What am I supposed
to do?
I've never even
seen the script...
Don't you worry about that...
Basically, the dialogue
is all ad‐libbed...
and we'll give you any
directions that you'll need.
You can take it from there,
can't you Ichika? Okay?
(giggling)
Uh‐huh...
Tatenashi:
Now, let us begin!
Once upon a time...
in a faraway land...
there lived a young girl
who was called Cinderella.
Now, however... Cinderella
is no longer just a name.
Huh?
Tatenashi:
Now the name stands for...
delighting in defeating
countless swarms
of enemy soldiers!
In myriad ballrooms
throughout the land.
The world's most
powerful warriors...
those with an appetite
for total destruction.
And the title that is most
befitting for those brave
lady warriors is...
"Strike Force Cinderella"!
Uh, what?!
Tatenashi:
Now, watch these young ladies
dance as they all vye
for the military secrets
that are hidden
within the prince's crown!
(cheers and applause)
Uh... huh?
Tatenashi:
And now, once again...
the night of the
blood‐thirsty Cinderellas...
is about to begin.
That crown is MINE!
(stumbling, groaning)
Just hand over that crown,
and no one will get hurt!
Ah!
(whimpers) Gah!
What would you do if you
really killed me?!
Tatenashi:
Don't worry.
They're all made
from safe materials.
I doubt that!
Rinin:
Hyaaah!
Ichika:
(cowers)
Hey, I can see
your underwear...!
AHH!
Are you out of your
freaking mind?!
You're wearing
glass slippers!
Don't worry...
they're made of
tempered glass.
Hey! This is dangerous!
Hey, wait!
Come back here!
Hey, that was a sniper rifle...
Has Cecilia gone crazy too?!
Stupid question!
Man... what the heck
is up with this play?!
Dash, got away...
I've been thinking about
who should have the right
to be roommates
with Ichika,
and I've decided...
I'm going to award
that to the person
who captures
the prince's crown.
Huh?
But I do not think
you can do that...
(chuckles) Don't worry...
with my authority
as the student council
president, I'll make it happen.
I swear that I will
win this challenge
no matter
what the cost!
Cecilia:
Ha! There you are...
I have you now!
Ichika, this way,
over here!
Oh, it's you... Hup!
Thanks, Charl...!
You really saved me!
I'm sure they are
right behind you...
so run like the wind!
Right. Thank you!
Oh, one moment please!
Charl:
Don't go yet!
But you said run!
Well, um...
it would really mean a lot
if you could leave the crown
here with me before you go.
Oh, yeah...
sure, no problem.
Tatenashi:
For the prince,
his country means everything.
So he can never lose
his crown, as it contains
confidential information...
For real...?
WAAAAAHH!
Tatenashi:
His sense of remorse triggers
a powerful electric shock!
Ichika?
Tatenashi:
Oh, bless his heart!
It's a tragic situation,
and the prince's love for his
country must truly be great.
It's agonizing!
But all we can do now
is watch over him!
Oh, my! It's a
tragic situation!
It's not necessary
for you to repeat that!
I'm sorry, Charl. But you
heard the crazy narrator,
I can't give
you the crown!
Huh?!
That is SO
not good!
Cecilia:
Hold it right there!
You've gone far enough!
Yeah, surrender now!
Watch out!
Oh...
AAAAAHH!
You get away from HIM!
Ichika? Ichika,
where are you?
Ichika:
It's dark... I can't breathe...
I don't know where I am.
Did I die just now?
Ahh!
What is this? It's so soft.
A‐ahh...!
Ahh!
Ichika! What were you doing,
down under there?!
Ugh...
well... uh...
Oh, that's right!
I'd better run!
Sacre bleu...!
Ichika, come back!
I wonder if this
is far enough...
Huh?
No!
I've waited for you.
And now your crown
is going to be mine...
Hyaah!
Ichika:
Hey! Watch‐
Gahh! Calm down!
Hey! Be careful!
Jeez!
You are my bride,
so give it up already!
But ya know...
love's no fun without obstacles.
Laura!
This looks bad!
C'mon, Laura! Let's go!
Ichika:
HOLY CRAP!
Ichika...
Bye!
Wait...
(whispers)
Hey! Ichika!
Ichika, this way!
Ah! Houki, am I glad
to see you!
Up here. You'll be
safe at the top.
Huh? Oh great...
we're climbing.
Ah! Ichika, you better
not be looking up!
Huh?
Look at what?
YOU KNOW WHAT!
Stop looking!
Hey, cut it out! You're supposed
to be rescuing me! Ack!
Both:
(panting)
Ichika:
How could I ever
thank you...?
Ahem...
Well... why don't you go ahead
and hand that crown over to me.
What?
Sorry, dear... It's not
going to be that easy.
Both:
Huh?
Ahhh!
Let's get outta here!
Uh‐huh! Ahhh!
Oh, man...! This is just
getting ridiculous!
Uh‐huh!
In the side pocket!
Whew, that was
a close one...
Yeah, but would you please
remove your hand now?
Huh? Oh! Sorry
about that.
(sighs) What I don't get
is why everyone wants
this stupid thing...
W‐well, that's because...
because... um...
Laura:
There you are!
That crown will be mine!
In your dreams!
What do you think
you are doing?
Eliminating
interlopers!
That's my line!
Hey, come on, you two!
Isn't anyone else tired of this?
Not yet!
I have ways of making you back
off, you bride‐stealer!
You just go ahead
and try it!
Uh, excuse me...
Hyaaaaaahh!
(surprised and startled moaning)
You... LOOK
AT THEM!
HYAAAAAAA!
I will not let you
touch my bride!
All:
(whimpering)
And now, it's time for
the audience participants
to join the story!
Tatenashi:
Come on, girls,
do your best trying to
capture the prince's crown!
Get through to me,
sweet, Orimura!
Let's make it happily ever after
with me, my prince!
Hey! Give me that crown!
AHHHH!
Wait, Orimu! Come back!
Gwha?! GAAAAAAHHH!
Reiko:
Shh... they won't
find you in here.
Thank you very much.
Hey, wait. Aren't you that
Miss Makigami I met earlier?
Yeah... I thought I should
use this opportunity
to take your
Byakushiki from you.
Huh?
I'm saying...
just give it to me already!
GAH! Ugh...
(coughing)
(strained)
So, who are
you, really?
Who am I... you ask?
A mysterious beauty,
disguised as...
a corporate
businesswoman!
Gosh... aren't you lucky?
Byakushiki!
I've been waiting so long...
for you to summon that!
Cecilia:
Good day to all of you!
This is the United Kingdom's
representitive, Cecilia Alcott.
And I'm announcing an initiative
that will make all of your
dreary lives just
a little bit better!
And all you have to do is cast
your ballot for Cecilia Alcott
as the IS Academy's
top candidate!
That's Cecilia Alcott!
Now, don't forget!
What?! Miss Orimura?!
Chifuyu:
Next time on Infinite Stratos 2,
"The Mysterious Lady"!