(Girls fuming)
Uh...
Well?!
Ehhh...
There, there, Rin,
please calm down.
Look... You are
scaring Kanzashi.
[Laura] Halt, Charlotte.
Stop this now.
(Kanzashi whimpers)
Under normal circumstances I
would torture her or administer
a truth serum...
but I am suppressing
that urge for the moment.
Do not say such things, Laura.
[Charl]
Here. This is for you,
Kanzashi. You are probably
thirsty, no?
Huh...? Oh! Thanks so much!
Now tell us...
what is going on, hm?
(gasp)
[Houki]
Yeah! Spill!
What we want to get to the
bottom of here is whether
you and Ichika are‐
Whether the two of you
are actually dating?!
(gasp)
Uh, it isn't like that...
with me and Ichika...
(growling)
You said "Ichika"!
You're on a first‐name
basis, too?!
[Kanzashi]
It's kinda hard to explain...
it's not that I don't hope that
something happens...
but so far, in real
life we're not like that...
(Rinin, Houki, Laura,
Charl & Cecilia sigh, laugh)
It looks like we read rather
too much into it, didn't we?
[Houki]
Yeah, sorry about the Spanish
Inquisition, Sarashiki.
Uhm, You... can call me
Kanzashi... if you like?
Cool! Then you can call us
by our first names, too.
Mm, okay.
And since we all happen to be in
the same grade,
why do we not get together
after school for the
practical training?
[Kanzashi]
Mm... hm...! Sounds like fun!
(nervous)
[Yamada]
Sorry to keep you
waiting, Orimura.
Everyone should be down
here soon... And here's
your special measuring tape.
A measuring tape?
So what exactly am I
supposed to do with it?
Really..?
That's for taking
body measurements.
In the wake of attacks by
unmanned units,
we realized we must improve
our IS suits, and precise body
measurements will be vital.
I understand that..!
The issue I'm
asking about is why
I'm the one who has to
take the measurements?!
Well, I had my doubts about
this idea at first, too...
but the student council
had already voted it through,
so here we are...
(stammering) HUH?!
(sinister laughter)
What the heck could
this ridiculous school
be thinking?!
[Chifuyu]
What are you gibbering
on about now, you bonehead?
Huh?
Big Sister Chifuyu!
Waaahhh!!
That's Miss
Orimura, here.
Ow...
I don't know why you can't
just follow through
with your assigned duties
like you're supposed to.
[Ichika]
Come on! This is clearly
not a regular duty!
I was set up!
Do you have to be such a
martyr about everything...
Besides, I may have just
the solution for you.
Whoa...! A blindfold!
My work is done.
[Ichika, thinking]
Thank you, Big Sister Chifuyu!
Thank you, Miss Orimura!
(gasp) It's see‐through...!
Noooo! Grrr...
Hey, look it's Orimura.
Oooo, is he really the one who's
taking our measurements?
[Nohohon] Yoohoo, Orimu!
Now... Everyone
please quiet down...
If each of you will strip down
to your unmentionables, we'll
start the measuring, okay?
Uwahhhh!
I'll be in the back area
recording the numbers that
you call out,
so whip out that measuring
tape and get started.
Uh... Hey, Miss Yamada,
wait... No, no, no! Come back!
Number one, Kiyoka Aikawa.
Ready or not, here I come!
Wh‐whoa! Wait just
a minute, I‐I...!
[Aikawa] Tee‐hee!
It's already too late!
Measure me, measure me!
UUUWWWAAAHH!
[Ichika, thinking]
What to do, what to do?
I'll do it without looking!
I'll use my mind's eye,
my third eye!
Excuse me, Orimura...
[Ichika] All right!
[Aikawa] Oh!
Now...! First... I'll
put the tape around...
so just hold
your arms out.
Ohhh‐kay!
(giggling quietly)
Let's see... around here?
[Aikawa] Oh!
(Ichika gasps)
[Aikawa] Uh! (reactions)
[Ichika, thinking]
That was not what I
thought it was... Uh...
[Aikawa]
Orimura! Hey! What do
you think you're doing?!
(embarrassing moans)
[Ichika]
I have no idea! I just want to
loop the measuring tape around
your back! I can't!
[Aikawa]
You're way off target! Aah!
[Ichika]
Then what is this? It feels
kind of soft and squishy. And
that's so not good.
[Aikawa] Hey, Orimura! Would you
please stop doing that!
[Ichika, thinking] Think about
flowers and summer...
[Ichika] Huh?!
[Aikawa] Ahhh!
Ichikaaaaaa!!! You're DEAD!!
What on earth are
you doing to her?!
Non! I cannot believe it!
So. Do you have any
last words, Ichika?
(advancing cries)
No, I was just doing
what they told me...
[Ichika] AAAAAAAAAAAAAAGGHHH!!!
[Cecilia]
I'm shocked.
My lovely waist has increased
by five millimeters. (sad)
Yeah well, I've put on some
weight, too, but... my chest
size stayed the same...
(angry) Distortion of body means
distortion of mind.. I must
increase my training time!
Man, girls sure do worry about
crazy things, huh? Chomp!
(eating) And I can't tell
any of that by looking at you.
Oh! How could you be so
insensitive toward us,
Ichika...?
By the way...
What is that you're
having for lunch today?
You seem to
be enjoying it.
Ulp! Ah, the bento Houki
gave me this morning.
(gasp)
(seething)
That was very
sneaky of you.
Sneaky and completely
unexpected.
I.. just happened
to make too much...
And her mistake is my pleasure,
because Houki's chicken breasts
are incredible. Chomp!
Oh..! Do you really
think so? (giggle)
(seething)
Of course, when it comes to
pork, Rin is just awesome.
(defeated)
And Charl's Pot‐au‐feu
is oh la la.
Everybody here is
a wonderful cook.
Uh... Ichika... what
about my cooking?
(gasp) Oh! Cecilia,
you're, uh...
[Rinin] Hey! I think it's about
time for her to hear the truth,
so you've got to tell her.
Cecilia's cooking is
like chemical warfare!
What? There's no way
I could say that!
But it would be for the
good of all mankind!
Hey...! I demand to know
what you two are whispering
about over there...
Ichika, I asked you
what you thought about
my cooking, now answer!
Bonjour! I am sorry
to be late...! And
Kanzashi is here, too.
Um, hello everyone.
[Ichika]
Hey, Kanzashi! Haha.
Come sit next to me.
(Cecilia whimpering)
Let me thank you in advance..!
I will sincerely appreciate it!
Ce‐cilia?!
I've decided that, in
order to improve my own
culinary abilities,
I want to learn more about
the cuisine from everyone
else's home countries.
Furthermore, since your
bento boxes are always fantastic
to look at and to eat..
I'd love for you to
teach me how to cook.
Uh... I see... It certainly
makes me feel good to
hear that...
So I'd be glad to
help if you insist.
Thank you so very much...!
All right, the first think
I'd like you to teach me
is how to prepare fried chicken!
(squawking)
Uh...?
What is.. that for?
[Cecilia]
That is a premier grade
Bresse capon chicken.
I assure you I had the
best one sent to me.
Actually, I have chicken in
the fridge... so you can take
that home, okay.
[Cecilia]
Oh, is that so? That's too bad.
But, I guess there's always
Christmas pie... isn't there?
(squawk)
Okay, let's get
started then.
[Houki]
But first, let's cut the chicken
thigh into bite‐size pieces.
Then, add some salt and
let it sit for a while.
[Cecilia] Mm‐hm...
[Houki]
Next, we'll prepare the garlic
and ginger that we'll be drop
in, okay?
[Cecilia] Okay!
[Houki] Not literally.
[Cecilia] Huh?
Nevermind, just
warm up the oil.
Okay...! Ahh...
Not like that!
[Houki]
Now it's time to remove
them from the oil.
After that, we're going to
let them rest for about
three minutes, okay?
(phone ringing)
[Houki] Oh! I'm sorry. But you
can take it from here, right?
Huh?
[Houki]
Oh, yes... I understand.
But actually, I'm pretty
busy right now...
Hm...
[Cecilia]
I'd really like it if the
presentation were just a little
bit more colorful...
And then, I'll add a spritz
of perfume for aroma.
Ah! Plus some of this and a dash
of that for the glaze...
So, is it done?
Yes! I just completed
the finishing touches.
[Houki]
Whoa! It came out
looking pretty good.
(giggle) Please do
have a taste.. Go on.
[Houki] Chomp!
Apparently, Shinonono isn't
feeling well, so she won't
be joining us today.
That's weird? Houki's
never called in sick.
Wonder why.
She sounded fine when I spoke to
her on the telephone last night.
Thank you in advance!
I do sincerely appreciate it!
Mm! No problem at all...
I just got some ingredients
earlier for pot‐au‐feu so I
can make some for Houki.
We can make it together.
So, what happened
to Laura today?
Shhhh! She seems to be
exhausted. She went to bed
as soon as she came home.
So, let us try
not to wake her.
Cecilia, would you make
the diagonal slits on the
sausages...?
That would be most helpful.
Oh? You mean like this?
Oui, c'est tres bon! You seem
to know what you are doing!
(giggle) Houki taught me how
to do this just yesterday.
Huh...?! So... Houki has given
you a cooking lesson as well?
Yes! It was all going along
quite nicely,
then for some reason she seems
to have suddenly fallen ill.
Oh... did she now?
I wonder why...
[Cecilia]
I really can't imagine...
But I'm certain that this
pot‐au‐feu we're preparing is
going to make her feel much
better.
Don't you think so?
Uh‐huh... I.. agree.
[Charl, thinking] Do not tell me
Houki got sick because she ate
Cecilia's cooking...
Surely, I am reading too much
into this, non? There has been
no problem so far anyway.
(humming merrily)
[Charl, thinking]
Besides, we are
cooking together...
[Charl]
Ah! There we go.
You just have to let it
simmer this way for a while.
[Cecilia] It looks scrumptious.
(Laura screaming in background)
[Charl & Cecilia] Huh?
Oh, excuse me one moment...
will you keep an eye on the pot?
[Cecilia]
What's going on?
Whenever Laura has a bad dream,
she tends to thrash around
and throw things.
It needs more...
color...
Ah... sorry about
that, Cecilia..
it looks like Laura went
straight back to sleep.
[Cecilia]
That's quite all right.
In any case, I believe
it's finally ready to eat.
Whoa! C'est magnifique!
Let us have some.
(giggle) Please,
go right ahead.
(rousing from sleep)
(waking up)
[Laura]
I must have been taking a nap
during the odd hours...
That is Charlotte there...
apparently she is sleeping...
(stomach growling)
Oh...
Oh?
What is this...? Charlotte made
this for me! Wunderbar!
[Ichika]
Charl and Laura are both absent
as well?
Do you think there's
something going around?
I'm not sure, but I do know that
Laura went to bed terribly early
yesterday evening.
[Ichika]
Now that I think about it, when
I went by to check on Houki
yesterday,
she would only tell me she was
okay from behind the door.
[Cecilia]
I wonder if it could be because
of something she ate.
Huh...? Cecilia.. did
you hurt you fingers?
Huh...?! What..? Oh, this?
It's nothing to worry about!
[Ichika] Oh...
[Cecilia]
Um, by the way, Ichika!
Would you.. like to join
me for lunch tomorrow?
I shall prepare a picnic lunch
for us and bring it with me.
What...? Well, umm...
I.. don't mind lunch
(awkward laugh) Sure, we
can eat lunch together...
Ohhh, hah, then I'll see you at
lunch tomorrow on the rooftop!
[Ichika]
Uh, okay then...
[Kanzashi]
Hi, Ichika...
Hey, Kanzashi... How are you?
Actually, I was, uh, cooking
and made too much for lunch...
So... I was wondering if you'd
like to have some?
(Cecilia gasp)
Man, this is so cool!
Her lunch box is a truly
magnificent work of art...!
I will never be able to
compete against that!
So. Are you saying that you want
me to teach you how to make
sweet and sour pork?
Yes, I do, Rin. Truly!
Are you kidding me?!
[Rinin, thinking]
Cooking WITH Cecilia?!
That has to be the most deadly
combination in the world!
Please! Today's the only
time we can do it.
But I really
don't want to die!
Oh, please!
Please help me, Rin! You're
the only one I can count on!
[Rinin, thinking]
A long time ago, I was a pretty
bad cook myself,
so I'd like
to help her out, but then...
Oh, no way! She's a deadly
weapon! One tiny slip could
be a fatal mistake!
(Gasp) Hold on...
[Rinin]
What's wrong with your fingers?
(Gasp) Oh, this..
happened..
when I was practicing
cutting with a knife...
But... It's really not
a big deal at all.
Mm...
All right then, I'll do it!
I'll teach you how to make
sweet and sour pork..!
But remember, you have
to taste your own food!
[Rinin]
So, now that we've
fried the pork,
the next step will be to
sauté the vegetables.
You mean like this?
Hey! It's looking good.
This is when I would normally
crank up the heat
until the flames came
leaping out, but...
'Til the flames
are leaping out?!
That's right. Chinese food
is all about firepower!
[Rinin] Anyway, we can't have
flames with an electric stove...
Let me handle that!
Huh?
[Rinin] Uh...! AAAHH!
I'm sorry, Ichika... but I
wasn't able to prepare the
bentos for us last night
because,
for some reason or other...
the food exploded...
Uh... exploded?
I'm especially disappointed,
because I was really looking
forward to watching you enjoy my
cooking, too...
[Ichika]
Well why don't we go make
something together right
now, okay...?
We don't have to buy our lunch.
And I'll teach you how to
make... my favorite dish!
Huh?
[Ichika]
Cecilia... are you
ready for this?
[Cecilia]
Uh, yes...! But I
am rather nervous.
[Ichika]
Look, Cecilia... we
don't have to do this...
if you don't feel comfortable.
[Cecilia]
No, I can do this!
We're already here.
[Cecilia]
I'll be fine.
[Ichika]
Okay then. Now, take
it in both hands...
and hold it gently...
[Cecilia]
Gasp! It's so very warm.
[Ichika]
Mhmmm... Then you wet it
thoroughly, like this...
[Cecilia]
Mm‐hm. Like this...?
[Ichika]
Yeah, I like that. All right
then, let's do it.
[Cecilia]
Uh, okay.
So... like this?
[Ichika]
Uh‐huh. And now you
can pick your filling.
[Cecilia]
What are those
red thingies there?
Oh those? Those are
pickled plum... Try one.
(Gasp) Chomp.
(reaction to sourness)
[Ichika] (laughter)
[Ichika]
Next, you press the rice into
a triangle shape, like this.
[Cecilia]
Let's see. Is this right?
[Ichika]
No, You have to squeeze
it a bit more gently.
(Ichika chuckles)
Hey! Were laughing
at me just then?!
[Ichika] I'm sorry.
[Ichika]
You were just... so cute.
Ah? You thought that I was cute?
That's hard to believe.
[Ichika]
Hey, let's try something?
(Cecilia gasps)
So.. The key is to squeeze
it in firmly and tight.
[Cecilia] Uh‐huh...
[Ichika]
There! Now it's done.
Ah! Could you please.. show
me how that went again?
(Ichika chuckles)
[Cecilia]
It's so lovely and warm...
[Ichika]
Well sure. It's
freshly made rice.
[Cecilia]
Oh, that's not what I meant...
Mhm. Honestly...
[Tabane]
Yummy! Mmm! These ribs
are delicious!
[Tabane] Chomp! (chewing)
[Tabane]
Ah! Wiiiine! (wacky sounds)
[Squall]
So is everything to your
liking, Doctor Tabane?
Mm.. I guess so. Except for that
soup that had the sleeping drug
in it, ya know...? Hee‐hee! Ah.
[Squall]
Now, as to the matter about
providing Phantom Task with
IS units...
Have you made any
decisions yet?
[Tabane]
(giggle) No way! Sounds like
a major pain..! Hey, bring me
some cake!
[Squall]
(laughing) Ah... I wonder what
you think about this then.
[Tabane]
Hehe!
Yah!
Uh‐oh!
[Tabane]
Does my hair look okay?
You see, I'm mentally
and physically over‐engineered,
down to the cellular level.
(giggle)
[Tabane]
As it is, I'm afraid that
Chi‐chan's about
the only one who's good enough
to challenge me physically.
[Tabane]
(laughing) Sorry,
E for effort though.
[Madoka] Don't move!
[Tabane]
Huh?
(evil chuckle)
[Tabane]
Ooo My...
Now this is interesting...
(Tabane giggles)
[Tabane]
Huh? Huh...?!
[Tabane] (laughter)
Okay so, what's your name?
Or... how about
I just guess?
[Tabane]
Let's see, could it be
Madoka... Orimura...
(Madoka gasps)
[Tabane]
Gahaha, I win! Hehe! Yay for me!
Oh! I don't mind making a
personal IS for this one.
[Madoka] Huh?
[Tabane]
And that means...
you get to come with me now.
Okay, lemme keep her!
Lemme keep her! Please!
Lemme keep her!
[Squall]
Sorry, but could be problematic.
[Tabane]
Aw, what a bummer!
You're so stingy. Oh, well...
[Tabane]
So, Madocchi‐wawa, what kind
of personal IS do you want?
A long‐distance type?
A close‐combat type? Or how
about a special‐armored type?
Well, I guess we can talk about
that later. I can hardly wait
to introduce you to Ku‐chan.
It'll be great! Haha!
Riiight! All right! Let's go get
something to eat! YAAY!
[Yamada, voiceover]
Right...! Now I'd like to begin
the special after‐school class.
(giggle)
What's the matter?
Are you feeling nervous?
You know, you really are
going to have to focus!
You. Need. To. Try. To. Fo‐cus!
(gasp) Miss Orimura?
[Chifuyu, voiceover]
Next time on Infinite Stratos 2,
"Looking for Memories".