(battle cry)
Cecilia:
I have this flank covered!
Charl:
Not yet! A little more!
Houki:
No!
Ichika!
Ichika:
Chifuyu...
(struggling)
White Knight:
I'll kill you...
Ichika Orimura.
Huh?!
Ichika:
(stammers)
Laura:
(sighs)
Is it morning now?
Laura, you again...!
But today...
I am not naked!
Ichika:
What the heck are you wearing?!
A brilliant assistant
instructor's recommendation.
If I were you, I think
I'd fire that instructor...
There is a special reason
why I was waiting here
for you to wake up...
Read this.
What is this?
Let's see here...
Ichika:
Come to end of the
summer festival for your
dating... pleasure?!
Ichika:
Hey! Is this event
at that big, swanky waterpark
that just opened up?!
I've really been wanting to
check this place out!
Is that right?
You want to go?
Look... It says here that
you can even rent a yukata
at the festival square.
I would like to wear a yukata...
together with you, Ichika...
Then why don't we
take everyone there and...
(yelps)
Hmph.
What was that?
Why is she so mad?
(content sigh)
Chelsea:
Milady, may I express
my gratitude for your
service in England
Chelsea:
during your summer break.
Your country thanks you.
Cecilia:
As a member of the Alcott
family, it's my duty to serve.
But more importantly...
I am here for
my triumphant return!
Triumphant because,
at the end of the day
I intend to be under the same
sky with my special someone.
Ichika:
Huh?
My beloved.
Ichika:
Oh hey, Cecilia!
I‐Ichika.
(giggles)
Is it possible that he
came out here just so
he could greet me?
(gentlemanly laugh)
Oh, my darling!
I couldn't sit still knowing
that you were coming back to me!
Oh, Ichika...
you naughty boy!
We shouldn't do that out here
where everyone can see!
Cecilia? Cecilia?
(gasps)
I‐I'm alright.
I was just feeling a little
bit dizzy, that's all
I see, you're okay then.
By the way, would you
like to go here tomorrow?
Oh! You're asking me
to go out with you, Ichika?
Yes! I, Cecilia Alcott,
shall make all of
the necessary preparations!
Laura:
Verdammt! He must become more
aware of his duties as my bride.
It seems like something
is bothering you.
Huh...? Oh, no.
It's nothing.
I know!
Why don't we go do a
little clothes shopping today
if you have time?
What for? The military
supplies all my clothing...
Charl:
That is a military uniform.
The summer break
is almost over. Let's go!
(sighs)
Well, I guess you
have a point.
So, can you be ready
to leave around 10?
Uh! Ja, that
is fine.
Laura:
I changed!
Here is my going‐out attire.
Charl:
But you're still
wearing a uniform!
Girl A:
Hey guys!
Have you heard the rumor
about the special crêpes
at the seaside park?
Oh, yeah, I have!
Supposedly, if you eat
mixed berry crêpes with
the person you like,
Girl B:
you'll find true love!
Girl A:
That's right! But I heard that
they're always sold out of them.
Charl:
Find true love with
the mixed berry crêpes?
Brain freeze!
Rinin:
Aw, tomorrow will be the last
day of the summer break...
It would be nice to make some
memories with Ichika...
Because of him, I chose to stay
here instead of going back home.
So you'd think that he could've
asked me out at least once.
Ichika:
Hey, Rin...
Ah! I‐Ichika?!
Ichika:
I'm coming in.
Ah, uh, just a...
just a second!
Uhhh...
(nervous laugh)
(screams)
(pained scream, groan)
Ichika:
(whimpers)
Huh?
Store Manager:
Welcome, ladies.
(gasps)
(customers fawning)
Store Manager:
Ooh! A platinum and a blonde...
Ah! I meant to say...
How would you ladies
like to try on some items
from our
latest collection?
Hmmmmm?
It's so sheer, that what's
underneat will be...
Uh... what do
you think, Laura?
Um... it is
very white...
Laura:
That is not bad,
but as you can see...
I'm already wearing white.
Why don't you
try it on?
No, it's too‐
Oh it's not
too much... bother!
Perhaps I am
mistaken about this...
(sighs)
but maybe I am simply not
attractive to the opposite sex.
(sighs)
This is absurd.
But... maybe I should have been
wearing garments that are
much cuter than this.
Ja, I am sure that Ichika would
commend me for that.
(German accent)
Laura, your clothes
are super cute.
Only my clothing?
The person who's wearing it,
is the cutest of all.
You foolish boy!
Charl:
So, did you
try it on, Laura?
What is this?
You're still
in your uniform!
Ah, actually...
I see, I guess you did not
find that one to your taste.
No, it is not that
I did not like it...
Actually...
I want something cuter.
Oh?
Oui! C'est si bon!
You want something cute, right?
Tell me what
kind you'd like.
Well... one that's a little
more revealing would be nice.
(chuckles)
Leave it to me!
(customers fawning)
Charl:
And the icing
on the cake...
You brought some shoes too.
You thought of everything.
Ha... but of course!
(struggling to keep balance)
You okay?
Ja, I am sorry.
Store Manager:
Quick, take a picture?
(customers fawning)
No problem!
(giggles and cheers)
(nervous laughter)
(sighs)
Oh... I don't believe it...
I think my boobs
got bigger AGAIN!
Ichika:
Houki? Are you in there?
I‐Ichika!
Houki:
Wh‐what do you want?
I've been looking
for you, Houki.
Can we talk?
Houki:
(stammers)
Okay! Just give me a second!
Uh, what do you want?
Uh! I'm sorry. I guess
you were in the shower.
Yeah, I was! So what did
you want to talk about?
Ichika:
Would you like to go
to this with me?
Houki:
What's this? Oh!
I know it's kind of last minute.
So you don't have to go.
Sure, I'm easy!
(uneasy laugh)
Cafe Worker:
Thank you for waiting.
(sighs)
I am so tired.
I really think that you should
have kept the dress on, Laura!
Mmm... I didn't want to because
I did not want to get it dirty.
Mmm‐hmm... or do you
just want Ichika to be
the first person to see it?
Oh! Nein! That
is totally untrue!
Excuse me, ladies.
Want a job?
Huh?
Charl:
Uhh... Madame, I was wondering,
why did you want me
to be dressed up as a butler?
Umm... because you're
better‐looking and more stylish
than most of
the guys around here.
Is that so...?
Charl:
But I wanted to wear
that kind of outfit...
Huh?
(sighs)
I guess this is just
inevitable for me?
Don't worry, toots.
It really suits you.
Yeah, so I've been told.
(laughs)
(door opens)
Hello! Welcome
to Café at Cruise!
Charl:
Thank you for
waiting, ladies!
Which one of you
ordered tea?
Customer:
O‐oh, I had the tea...
(flustered shudders)
Charl:
Very well then,
just let me know if you
require anything else, ladies.
Please enjoy!
Robbers:
(panting)
Manager:
Hello! Welcome to‐
(screams)
Alright, nobody move!
Shut up, yous!
Attention, you've been
completely surrounded!
Give up and turn yourselves in
peacefully, I repeat...
If you want the hostages
to be released unharmed,
bring us a car!
And don't even think
about putting some kind
of tracking device in it,
or trying to follow us!
(hysterical screaming)
(chuckles)
They look pretty scared!
Robber C:
Hey, blondie!
Yeah! You over there!
I'm thirsty.
Bring me the menu.
What the hell
is this?
Laura:
It's water.
Huh? Water?
Go ahead and drink it...
...if you can that is.
(battle cry)
Don't mess with us,
you little brat!
I'll murderize ya!
Unfortunately for you,
there's more than one of us!
Too bad for you!
Target number two, neutralized.
And you, mon ami?
No problem.
Target number three,
also neutralized.
Robber B:
(struggling)
This is a bunch of crap!
How'd we let these kids
do this to us?!
You're so slow... now die!
All targets neutralized.
They saved us!
Thank you for saving
our lives, Maid and Butler!
Um, Laura, it'd be a
problem if they find out
that we're the
representative contenders!
We should get
out of here, now!
A good point.
We should probably leave.
Robber A:
I didn't come this far to get
caught and spend the rest
of my life in jail.
I'd rather blow everything
here all to Hell!
That's Checkmate!
C'est fini?
Unless you want me to blow off
your amrs or something.
Excuse moi!
Can I have two crêpes
with mixed berries?
Aw, bummer, ladies!
I'm afraid there's no more
mixed berries today.
What? You're
sold out?
So, do you
still want one?
Ja!
I want one with strawberries
and blueberries, now!
Huh?
Straw' and blue? No problemo!
This is really good!
Ja. This is my very first time
to eat a real crêpe.
and I am finding it
to be quite tasty.
I'm going to come here
with Ichika next time.
It'd be so nice if they have
the mixed berries crêpes...
Mm... Charlotte.
Uhh... oui?
Uh! L‐Laura...
What was that about?!
There was sauce on your cheek.
I understand,
but still...
Both of my hands were engaged.
However, if you are going to be
upset, I will offer you a bite
of my crêpe as a peace offering.
Merci beaucoup,
Laura...
Laura:
By the way,
about the crêpe shop...
They do not have
the mixed berries crêpes.
Ah?
Laura:
It wasn't even
on the menu.
Furthermore, I did not see any
sauce on the shelf that was
labeled for that purpose.
Oh is that right?
You are so observant!
But you still got to eat
the mixed berries crêpe, ja?
Oh yeah! Strawberries
and blueberries!
Mmm! Together!
Sacré bleu!
Now I understand the real reason
they are always sold out of the
mixed berry crêpes!
Laura:
What is this
bizarre contraption?
Are you sure
these are pajamas?
Mmm! Ah! Sacré bleu!
And you look so good
in them mon petit cher!
Laura:
Do not hold me that way!
I cannot move!
Charl:
Now, behave!
You're a little pussycat so you
need to sit still on my lap!
Charl:
Can you just say "meow"?
That's a good pussy!
I will not comply!
Why would I ever want to do
something so embarrassing!
Why would you?
Because it's so cute!
Come on, now!
Say it with me!
"Meow".
Ah... Ah...
Meow...
Très adorable
(door knocks)
Oui, who is there?
How's it goin'?
Well, those are
unusual outfits.
Black cat and a white cat, huh?
Oh yeah... about tomorrow...
Ichika:
Are you interested?
Huh?
(gasps)
(angry meow)
(sires wailing)
Announcer:
Intruder detected in Area 6‐D!
All units move to intercept!
Repeat, intruder detected
in Area 6‐D!
Intercept at once!
Squall:
Um, do you read me?
Let me make this clear,
your body has been
implanted with nano‐devices
that monitor
your every action.
Therefore, you will carry out
your mission as ordered.
There she is!
Vile pests!
Can't kill me yet?
How pathetic!
Good girl, M.
Let's see more.
This is a restricted area!
Is she gonna fight
us barehanded?!
There's a special IS
sealed up on this base...
A special Infinite Stratos.
It's mine.
It's what?!
Deploy!
That's Silent Zephyrus!
It can't be... Phantom Task?!
Houki:
(giggles)
I can't believe this...
Ichika was so direct about
asking... but I'd never imagine
he'd be so nervous when he
finally got up the nerve
to ask me out on a date!
But here we are and... huh?
Huh?!
Ichika:
Hi there! Good morning!
Sorry I kept
you waiting, everyone!
You idiot!
I feel so stupid for coming here
with such high hopes!
I should have known...
You fail
as a bride!
Jeez... what are
they so mad about?
Cecilia:
Oh yes! Let's hurry and get over
to the pool now, shall we?
Houki:
Haaaa Ichika!
Ichika! Come on!
Hurry up!
Ugh! He set us up!
Cecilia's the raunchiest!
I am not the raunchiest!
Charl:
Look over there!
It's a water slide for couples!
Houki:
I suppose I don't
have a choice...
I wouldn't object
to doing it with you.
Aikawa:
Yo‐ho‐ho!
Rinin:
I don't get it, where could
those two have gone?!
Ichika:
What the hell was
that all about?!
Houki:
Wh‐what?!
Charl:
You're such a pervert!
Ichika:
Huh?! It's not my fault!
Tanimoto:
Yeah, it's so nice!
Charl:
Mon Dieu! What are these?!
Houki:
Huh? You've never
seen them before?
Cecilia:
Are we going to eat octopus?
Charl:
Oh, no, no, no!
Nothing with tentacles for me!
Ichika:
And when that happens,
it's game over!
Houki:
Uh... wh‐what?
Laura:
Ja! This is pretty good.
Charl:
Don't worry, we're behind you!
Rinin:
Yeah well, I've had sniper
training in the military too,
ya know!
Ichika:
And another summer, gone.
Tatenashi:
It looks like
it's game time for me,
Team Leader:
Tatenashi Sarashiki...