[Kanzashi]
Could it be? That I
actually like Ichika?
[Ichika]
So would you like to be
my partner?
[Tatenashi] (Laughs)
I bet my unit's data
came in handy, right?
[Kanzashi]
This was... all her?!
Mm...
(Whimpering)
(Light sobbing)
(Courtyard chatter)
Okay... she's not here?
Hello, everyone...!
Today's the day of the IS
tag‐team tournament spectacular!
I want to see all of the
participants out there
She's not here, either...
put every bit of their
hard training to work
Where are you, Kanzashi?
and give this competition
everything they've got!
[Tatenashi]
And even if you don't have your
own personal IS unit right now,
I think this tournament is
going to be something you
can still learn a lot from.
So please pay close
attention, everyone!
(Laughs)
I bet my unit's data
came in handy, right?
(Gasp)
Uh... AH!
You don't have to do anything
at all, Kanzashi...
Because I'll handle
everything for you...
Wha‐?
But... but I... can do this!
(Giggle)
No, you should just
remain incompetent.
I won't...
(Tatenashi laughs)
NOOO!
There's no way...
I can't beat her.
But I have to go...
I have to.
Therefore, with the
hope that this experience
will be a worthwhile one,
I would like to declare this
tournament officially open!
And now that we've
dispensed with all the
required formalities...
It's time to announce the tag
team tournament match‐ups!
Oh!
Kanzashi! Where are you?!
Uh! Could she have
already gone down to
the pit by herself?
(Explosion)
AH!
Now what?!
UH! Miss Orimura!
We're under attack!
Hmph. What are those?
They look like the same
unmanned type as before.
No, wait... Those are
an advanced version!
How many?
Five, ma'am!
They appeared at
each arena's pit...
And now they're attacking the
students with personal IS units
who were standing by!
Damnit... This is
way too fast!
Huh?
Instructors, evacuate
the students...
All combat‐capable
instructors, prepare
to deploy!
Understood!
You're pretty bold,
all right...
But don't underestimate us!
Agh!
Huh?! What's up with her?!
[Cecilia]
Rin, get back!
UGH!
AH!
AHH!
Hng! HNNNG!
OHH!
Get down, Laura!
Ugh! Hnnnng... Aahhh!
Ch‐Charlotte!
Huh?!
(Gasp)
(Muffled squeak)
No. No!
What's happening?!
[Kanzashi]
No... help me...
Somebody, please...
Orimura!
[Ichika]
AAAGGHH!
Guh! Hng!
[Kanzashi](Whimpering)
Kanzashi! You okay?!
Hah... Orimura!
Activate your IS...!
You're in this now!
Okay! Uh...
Uggh! Huh?
Orimura!
Each shot...
has so much power...
Uh... Uh!
I wish I... I could...
...find the courage...
to fight beside you!
Hyaaaaaahh!
Let's push it outside
and get some distance!
[Houki]
Hagh! Hah!
Yaaggh!
[Tatenashi]
I gotcha now!
Ugh! This thing's really hard!
Hey, Houki! Activate the rear
armor, then give me a push!
Hm! Got it!
Hrragh!
I got your back!
Let's do it!
(Grunting)
What's the plan?!
We're going to break
through that unmanned
IS unit's armor!
But how...?!
We're just going to do it!
I wonder how you
like THIS move!
You ain't seen nothin' yet!
I still have a few
tricks up my sleeve!
Ah! The armor!
AAHH!
Houki... Ggghh...!
Ah! Now! Switch all your
settings to defense,
or it will suck you in!
But... you just...
I'm immortal...
Didn't you know that?
[Tatenashi]
Take this. Mysterious Lady's
maximum firepower!
No! Don't do it!
Now Mistilteinn spear...
ENGAGE!
Huh?! What's that?!
No! Don't tell me
Houki and the others‐
[Kanzashi]
Watch out!
Whoa!
I'll handle this!
Kanzashi?!
Orimura, go check the condition
of that gate over there!
You got it!
Hah! You're not getting
past me, you bitch!
[Yamada]
I'm detecting some type of
unknown energy emerging from
the enemy IS unit's arm!
And now we're experiencing
problems with the shield
barrier deployment!
Absolute defense
has been nullified!
Ugh...
That must be an
anti‐Infinite Stratos IS.
(Grunting)
Orimura!
Ahh!
(Gasp)
[Kanzashi]
(Scared whimper)
Ahhh!
(Panicked breaths)
No...
NOOOO!
How dare you?
How dare you?!
My sister!
NOOOOO!
AAGH!
DIE!
HYAAGH!
HYAAAAGH!
HYAAH!
(Grunting)
URGH!
(Charging up)
This ends NOW!
[Kanzashi]
The core!
If I blow that away...
(Clunk)
Huh?
Uh...
(Scared whimpers)
AAHHHH!
I‐Ichika?!
[Kanzashi]
Ichika!
Ahh!
Uhh...
Huh?
Please stop... No...
This is it...
I just... can't do it...
I'm not... good enough...
[Kanzashi]
Ichika... I'm sorry...
(Mechanical roar)
I couldn't help you...
I'm so useless.
I'm sorry...
that I was ever born...
In the real world...
there are no heroes.
They don't exist.
[Tatenashi]
AAGGHHH!
Ugn!
Ngh. Huh?
[Kanzashi]
Big sister?
(Gasp)
No... SIS...!
Big sister!
(Giggle)
How long has it been
since you've called me that?
I thought you were...
How did you...?
This is... impossible!
No, it isn't.
Yes, it is!
Because in this world...
there are no heroes!
[Ichika]
No, there aren't.
Huh?!
There's no perfect
invincible hero...
None.
Ichika...
The heroes from our
fantasies...
they never get to laugh..
and they don't cry either.
But I am human,
so I cry AND I laugh.
I lose sometimes, too.
But I don't give up...
And if the choice means losing
my friends, then I'll fight!
But aren't you...
Aren't you afraid of dying?
Of course I am...
But if I run away,
how could I ever be
able to live with myself?
(Sobbing)
Then I'm just...
I'm just...
I'm just a coward!
(Sobbing)
But who cares?
Does it matter?
If you're weak?
Or dirty?
Or have no courage?
You're still human.
But... But, Sis...
I wanted to be‐
It's all right,
my dearest Kanzashi...
No one's perfect.
The trick is
accepting that.
Accept your weaknesses,
and then you can beat them.
Because...
I'm just human?
That's right.
And besides,
you're my sister,
and I'm proud of you!
[Kanzashi]
Really?
I'll finish this
for you, sister!
This is a good luck
charm. Use it when
you really need it.
An aqua crystal?
Good luck... freshman.
Mm‐hm!
(Grunting)
Ichika, status report!
Answer me!
Ugh... Houki?
Can you use your
Reiraku Byakuya?
[Ichika]
No. I don't have
any more energy left.
Then I'll have to use
my Kenran Butou.
Agh!
But I've gotta
buy some time first!
[Kanzashi]
Don't worry!
I've got you covered!
Kanzashi!
There's no time
to debate this!
Hyah!
[Houki]
Ichika! Grab my hand!
(Charging up)
Hng!
Uchigane Nishiki...
Manual guidance system,
activate!
Ready Yama Arashi
warhead missiles,
one through forty‐eight!
Setting all trajectories
to manual control!
Uchigane Nishiki,
lend me your power!
NGH! It's still coming?!
Gah! Hrg!
Akatsubaki...
I'm counting on you!
Let's show 'em what we can do!
Okay! Enough with the
techno‐babble already!
That left arm is mine!
Finish it!
HAAAAAAAAGH!
Kanzashi! Now!
Mm!
It didn't work?!
It's time to use that charm!
(Snap)
Yay!
(Sighs of relief)
(Laughter)
(Sigh)
Cecilia!
Ahah!
Uh! Hah...
Hm!
Boo‐yah
(Crows cawing)
(Waking sounds)
[Kanzashi]
Huh! Big sister!
Ah! Kanzashi! Oww!
Please, try not
to move...
You could reopen
your wounds.
Yeah...
[Tatenashi]
I wonder how many years it's
been since the last time we
talked like this.
I guess I owe this
opportunity to Ichika.
Why did I ask him to do this?
Did I want to cling to him
and rely on his kindness?
[Kanzashi]
Big sister?
Oh! Uh‐huh?
Is something wrong?
Your face is really red.
Oh? It must
be because
of the sunset.
Uh‐huh...
Is that what it is?
Um, Sis?
Yeah?
I‐I'm sorry
about everything...
I mean, I'm such
a bad sister!
(Sobbing)
[Tatenashi]
That's not true.
Huh!
Actually, you are
my dearest little sister...
And you're growing up
to be so strong.
Oh, Big sister...
Big sister!
(Sobbing)
(Soft gasp)
[Yamada]
They turned out to be
advanced unmanned units
with unregistered cores.
We only managed
to get two of them.
Inform the government
that they have all
been destroyed.
But ma'am! If we do something
like that, the whole school
could be in jeopardy!
Don't worry...
Have you forgotten
who you're talking to?
I think I can
protect this school.
And as a matter
of fact...
I'd bet my life on it.
Right. This is it.
I have to let him know...
Just how I feel.
(Knock on door)
(Door opens)
[Ichika]
Oh, Kanzashi. What's up?
Well, um...
Here... This is
for you, Ichika.
What's this...?
Anime?
Um, yeah.
I don't know‐
Man, I used to watch
this all the time!
Hah!
You never know what you love
until you find it.
You too, huh?
Uh! Yeah...
Mm‐hm... Kinda...
I see!
[Kanzashi]
And I like... like...
Like... very much!
(Panicked panting)
[Ichika]
Huh? Uhh...
(Panting)
I said it...
I said I like Ichika!
It was okay, right?
I didn't say anything
that was too weird, did I?
[Ichika]
You never know what you love
until you find it.
You too, huh?
Mm‐hm... Kinda...
Wait! What'd I say?! Oh no!
I think I told him that
I liked anime, not him!
[Kanzashi]
♪Da‐da‐daaa‐la‐la‐la‐laaa!
La‐laaa!♪
♪It's so tasty!
So scrumptious!♪
♪And so healthy!♪
Kanzashi's late‐night
ramen snack!
We have three delicious flavors:
Salt, bean paste, and soy sauce!
Huh?! Miss Orimura!
You saw that, didn't you?
[Chifuyu]
Next time on Infinite Stratos 2,
"Cooking My Way".