Volt Texture...
Equip.
Medics to Blocks
8, 7 and 5, stat...!
Collect all wounded
and transport them
to the recovery center!
The second year's strongest four
are about to go head-to head.
The Carnival's grand finale...
This should be a hell of a show.
This semester's
top-ranked student
is currently being transported
from Block 11 to Block 12.
We still haven't seen
the top student yet?
So you've been saving
the best for last,
have you, Sister Margaret?
Perhaps.
Rank 1 is surrounded.
Six contestants closing in...
seven... eight... eleven total.
I realize these
matches are designed
to simulate real
battle conditions,
but this year's Carnival
is something else.
Can't say I've ever
seen one Pandora face
so many opponents at once.
It's not the sort of
thing you expect to see
from a second-year student...
...that's for sure.
Now deploying... Volt Weapon.
It's time for battle,
Nova Blood.
Three down... Now another two.
Rank 1 has eliminated
nine opponents.
The Untouchable Queen...
That is the title the
students have given her.
Although you may know her
as Satellizer el Bridget...
Bridget?
You don't mean that Bridget...
None other.
"Untouchable Queen"
is a rather odd nickname.
I think it will
make sense soon enough.
The fifth, fourth and
third-ranking students
are currently
en route to Block 3.
I'm bringing in the injured.
Are you ready?
Ready!
As you may know, the East
and West Genetics Academies
were founded as institutes
to prepare all
Pandora for their battle
against the extra-dimensional
creatures known as Nova.
You know all about
Pandora, I'm sure,
but let's cover the basics.
Kaho Hiiragi!
Is learning about the fate
of the world really
that boring to you?
Uh... No! I mean...
No, ma'am! Not at all!
In that case,
since you're a Pandora,
why don't you
tell us about them?
We Pandora are implanted
with Stigmata that give us
the power to equip Volt Textures
and deploy Volt Weapons.
That's what we use
to combat the Nova.
And what else... in addition
to our Volt equipment,
the Stigmata also give us
increased agility
and strength...
As far as the basics go,
I guess that's about it.
Well spoken for a first
year--you can take your seat.
The Stigmata also give their
user healing abilities...
They can reconstruct
a Pandora's body
by using her DNA as a guide.
Administer the
activating solution...!
If the Stigmata doesn't
activate quickly enough...
these injuries may
not heal properly!
Start neural array expansion
and optimization now!
Yes, Doctor Elise!
I don't want to see any
deaths at this Carnival!
Neural integration complete.
Synapse signal
transmission normal.
I need 1,000
milligrams of Savitcam.
In extreme cases,
like when a Pandora
loses one of her limbs,
the Stigmata can grow a new
one without even leaving a scar.
I would know...
Four years ago,
I experienced it myself.
Miss Yumi?
Yes? What is it, Arthur?
Before you became a teacher,
you were a Pandora
like the girls here, right...?
Could you tell us a little
bit about how that went?
Oh! I wanna know, too!
Me too! Yeah, me too!
You said you were
hurt four years ago...
I did the math and
that means you took part
in the Eighth Nova Clash...
That's when the Nova Type S
showed up in Japan, isn't it?
It was the Eighth Nova Clash...
Once again, the extra
dimensional creatures
entered our world...
Leaving nothing but
destruction in their wake.
Nova Type S detected
in the Uraga Channel...
Freezing initiated.
Radius: 220 meters.
All vessels in the area
have ceased movement!
Lost contact with all vessels!
At its current speed,
the Type S is expected
to reach Tokyo Bay
in 20 minutes.
We will encounter
the Nova in 20 minutes.
At Genetics we learned all
the skills we need to fight...
Now is the time to
put them to the test.
Yes, ma'am!
Yumi.
What is it? Where's Kazuha?
Back home...
She had something
to take care of first.
I see.
Of course... we fought
with all our strength,
but in the end,
it amounted to nothing...
It wasn't us who defeated
the Nova that day...
It was all her... Kazuha Aoi.
Kazuha! Kazuha!
Kazuya!
Don't go...! I can't lose you!
You're my only sister!
I need you!
What if those things kill you?!
Don't worry,
I promise I won't die...
I have something
special to protect me.
It's not just Stigmata
that I carry on my back...
I carry all of your
hopes and dreams as well.
We Pandora carry the hopes
and dreams of the whole world
because we're the only ones
who can defeat the Nova...
And all of those hopes,
give me strength...
That's why...
I promise I won't lose.
And that was the last time
I ever saw my sister...
Kazuha.
So long, sis. Wish me luck.
Hi, I'm Chiffon Fairchild,
the Student Council
President at West Genetics.
Uh, hi...!
Is something troubling you...?
No.
Then let me tell you a
little about the school...
I'd sure hate for you
to have a tough time
on your first day there.
Thanks.
All the second year
Pandoras will be looking
for partners among
the underclassmen,
so one of them might
ask you to be their Limiter.
Why do they pick
from the underclassmen?
An excellent question.
It's the Ereinbar.
The... what?
It's a little-understood
sensory organ buried deep
within the brain,
controlling sight, smell,
hearing, taste and touch.
When the Limiter and
Pandora synchronize in battle,
they share their Ereinbar...
making their five senses one.
Compatibility rates
differ between partners,
but younger boys tend
to do best overall.
So, there you have it...!
That's why Pandoras
always pick underclassmen
when they're
looking for a Limiter!
By the way, when a Pandora and
Limiter share their Ereinbar...
it's called an Ereinbar Set.
I wonder what that's like...
Activate Ereinbar Set!
Freezing!
Freezing areas are set.
Two minutes remaining!
Volt Weapon: Deploy!
No turning back now.
Let's do this.
The purpose of
the Ereinbar Set is
to neutralize the
Nova's Freezing Area.
Using their Limiter to create
a Freezing Area of their own,
the Pandora can then act
within the Nova's range.
I can see the Nova's core!
The neutralized
zones are shrinking!
All Pandora and Limiters
re-engage Freezing Areas!
Use your Ereinbar Set, hurry!
Hold on, Yumi!
90% of Pandora vital
signs have been lost.
Alert all standby medics.
Retrieving the Pandora
is our first priority.
Repeat, retrieving the
Pandora is our first priority.
No matter how hard we train,
fighting the Nova is
always a dance with death...
yet fighting is all we can
do if we want to survive.
Your sister believed
that as well...
And that's why she
fought without fear
until her own dance
came to an end.
It's Kazuha!
She saved us... saved everyone.
But all we could do was watch as
she sacrificed her own life...
You mean she died.
Despite her bravery,
that was only one battle in
a war that still rages on...
And that is why we
attend this school.
This is Control.
West 2-3,
you're clear to land...
Landing zone one is
wide open. Over.
West 2-3 to Control.
We're at a nice cruising speed
and proceeding
to landing zone 1.
Over.
Hi! Welcome to West Genetics!
I hope you had fun on your
big field trip today, Chiffon!
I did...!
That's my friend, Ticy Phenyl.
She's on the
student council too,
so you'll prob'ly
see her around a lot.
It's so nice to meet you!
Here we go!
I got you now!
Stay back...
I won't let you or
anyone else touch me.
Rank 3 is incapacitated...
Three of the top five
shot down in an instant...
They didn't stand a chance...
...couldn't lay a finger on her.
I see... It's just
like you said...
I had my doubts...
but you live up to your name...
You really are
untouchable, aren't you...
So... she's the famous
Untouchable Queen
we've been hearing about?
Satellizer el Bridget...
I expected no less
from our top student!
However, your reign is
about to come to an end!
For today, you will know
the bitter taste of defeat.
And who shall be the
one to serve it to you?
Why, me?!
Ganessa Roland, of course...
Hey... did you hear me?
Come back here!
Chains of Binding!
The training area up
ahead is used
for what we call the
"Carnival" where the Pandoras--
No fair...
What's the point
in getting stronger
if she's just gonna
get stronger, too?
Hey...! What are you
staring at you, creep?!
I... It's nothing, sorry.
It's you, isn't it...? Kazuha!
You're still alive!
Oh no... why did he have
to grab her, of all people?
Run away, Kazuya!
Hey, wait...
Why is she acting so shy
and cutesy all of a sudden?
Weird, isn't it?
I missed you so much...
Don't ever leave me again!
No... let go of me!
Stop it--I said stop!
Never... Never!
A Freezing Area?!
Why? What's going on?!
This fight isn't over yet!
I can't move!
The fact of the matter
is that I'm Rank 1
whether you like it not!
You have no right
to touch me like that!
You can use it, too?
Next time: "Pandora Mode."