Satellizer...! Rana! Ow--
They said you are not
supposed to get out of bed yet!
Oh... Right... Thank you.
I'm sorry...
I wanted to help you both,
but I only ended up
getting in your way.
You've got that right!
You entered a battle you had
no right to be a part of...!
What did you think
you were doing?!
You just barged in without--
If you were--!
If he had... suffered
a more serious injury...
Kazuya was thinking of you...
He is a hero...
Do you not understand that he
was trying to protect you...?
It is not right of you
to scold him for it!
Satellizer, wait!
I thought you were
very brave, Kazuya.
It is simply amazing
that the more I learn
about you the
more I find to like!
But--
The day will surely come
when you and I are bound
together in Baptism!
Baptism...? I dunno--
I know...
And it is all right if my
feelings are not returned.
At least that is...
for right now.
What's wrong with me?
I was actually happy
when he tried to help, but...
Oh, Kazuya.
Prom...? What's that?
It's a yearly event that we have
where all the students gather
in the auditorium and
dance the night away...!
I'm really looking
forward to it!
It used to be that
only upperclassmen
were allowed to attend,
but now they're letting
the first-years come, too!
It's designed to strengthen
the bonds between
existing partners...
or provide an opportunity
to find someone suitable...
That was why
they originally had it,
but it really serves
as a chance for everyone
to take a break
and have some fun!
Yeah, but you're
forgetting the best part...!
The Pandora Queen contest.
Pandora Queen?
It's a beauty pageant
that happens at the
end of the evening...
The winner's determined
by votes from the students.
Last year it was Miss Elizabeth
who earned the title.
Given her beauty
and natural grace,
I can't think of anyone more
deserving of the title "queen."
She definitely looks the part.
Yeah, you're right...
She really is
beautiful, isn't she?
Careful...!
You better not let you-know-who
catch you gawking.
How are things going with you
and the Untouchable Queen?
Fine... I guess.
Actually, things have
been pretty tense
since the other night...
I've hardly had a
chance to talk to her.
Really, Elizabeth...?
You're really not planning
on doing anything
about Satellizer?!
Well... both our fifth-ranked
and fourth-ranked girls
were unable to handle her.
Sorry.
We've no choice
but to face facts...
Her abilities are
clearly greater
than the powers we posses.
Are you trying to
say you admit defeat?
Rather than think in terms
of victory or defeat,
let's focus on the
previously unknown powers
you forced these
girls to demonstrate.
The possibilities
of those powers
are of great interest to me.
I'm reminded of something
Sister Margaret said...
"It may not be long
before these peaceful days
of ours come to an end"...
This is no time for Pandora
to be fighting one another...
Something terrible
may be looming
just ahead that
threatens us all.
You're saying we
need to preserve
our fighting potential...
That's so typical of you.
Based on everything
I've seen and heard,
Satellizer's abilities
are significantly
more powerful than
when I fought her.
That's a different
subject all together.
What I want to know is
how exactly we're going
to go about punishing her.
Taking into account that she
beat us last time... Right?
So you're all gonna hang your
heads in shame and back down?
What is your intent?
You're not suggesting
we go against Elizabeth?
You misunderstand me.
We don't have to fight her...
There are so many other
ways to teach her a lesson.
Right...
All I have to do
is go up to Kazuya
and say "I'm sorry,
I lost my temper."
Then I'm sure I'll
stop feeling this way.
Kazuya, hello...!
I have been wondering
where you were!
I was searching over
the entire campus for you!
You were?
I was...! I just overheard
that there was to be
some sort of school dance
held here next week...!
I would simply be overjoyed
if the two of us
could dance together!
Oh... Have you already
invited Satellizer
to be your partner
for the dance?
Well... no... No, not yet...
Then you will be
able to go with me!
Thanks, but... Uh...
Satellizer!
Oh...! Wow, will you
look at the time...
Right...!
I just remembered
something I forgot to do.
Don't leave me here!
Rana... I hate to
break it to you,...
Well, not really...
But Kazuya has
already invited me.
Huh?
How strange!
Because Kazuya just told me
that he had not invited you yet.
Come on, you two know better
than to start fighting here!
We are not fighting right now...
Unlike Satellizer,
I have enough sense
to know where fighting
is appropriate.
Then you know there's
no reason to fight now...!
Since Kazuya is my partner he'll
be going to the dance with me!
I didn't sign up for this.
I'm sorry, Rana.
Truth is...
I was already planning to
ask Satellizer to the dance.
So you have decided...
It seems I have no choice
but to accept my defeat.
What "defeat"?
However, I am not one
to give up that easily!
Oh dear god!
Kazuya...!
I'll let you know what
time to pick me up for prom.
Don't be late!
Yeah! I'll be there!
What's the count at?
We've got roughly seventy
votes from the first-years.
That's acceptable.
A lot of those new boys
don't have partners...
It should be easy
to entice them.
We've got a solid sixty votes
from the second-years.
I'm sorry, ma'am,
but the third-years
still favor Elizabeth...
We've only got twenty votes--
No excuses...
Get out there... and shore
up the third-year votes
no matter what it takes!
Yes... You can count on me.
I don't care if you
have to buy them...
if I don't find myself
standing among the finalists,
then I, Miyabi Kannazuki,
will never live with the shame!
I don't think this
one's right either!
What is wrong with that boy?
Getting all flustered
because of a kiss...!
Well, if I wanted to do
something like that...
Not that I do,
but... if I did...
...I could... do it
much better than her.
How could I even
think such a thing?
Oh no...! It's going
to start any time now!
Uh... Hold on...! I'm coming!
So... having a
good night so far?
I'm sorry, I was
just a little nervous.
We should probably get going.
I... agree.
You two just make
the sweetest couple.
Who's there?!
It's Attia Simmons...
The sixth ranked third-year...
The Architect of Evil!
Now that I've won the top spot
for my year at the Carnival,...
I'm going to turn my attention
toward becoming this year's
Pandora Queen as well!
With your beauty
and womanly charm...
I think the title of queen
suits you perfectly...
You're sure to win
the crown tonight!
Wow... I guess I should
turn my attention
to finding an eligible guy...!
Which reminds me...
I wonder if Kazuya's here yet.
Well... yet another
year has come and gone,
but here we are again...
Welcome one and all to the
West Genetics Promenade...!
Having fun?
I certainly hope
we can get through the
festivities without incident.
The current average is
roughly five or six ending up
in the nurse's office.
Chiffon...
Will Sister Margaret be
joining us this evening?
She was invited but
she never responded.
I see... I was
worried about that.
What do you mean?
There's been an increase
of dimensional fluctuations
that's way beyond anything
we've seen before.
When did this start?!
Does it have any relation
to the appearance of the Nova?
We have no idea.
Sister Margaret's been
busy taking meetings
with the military and Chevalier
concerning these very issues.
I suggest that we all take time
to enjoy the party
on her behalf.
Whatever you say, ma'am...
We'll do our absolute best.
It's been decided by
the third-years that the
punishment for Satellizer
el Bridget will be suspended.
Suspended?
Therefore, I'm not here as
a representative of my class,
but merely as an individual
student acting on my own...
And I've come here to
challenge you to a duel!
Another duel?!
Please don't do this!
Kazuya!
Forgive me...
I know you don't
want me to interfere...
But I have to do this, even
if it means you yell at me.
I can't stand by doing nothing
when you're in harm's way...
If I didn't feel that,
I wouldn't be worthy
of being your partner...
That's just the way it is.
Kazuya.
Oh, goodness...
You two clearly have no idea
what I'm getting at, do you?
I would detest seeing
our lovely prom
disrupted by bloodshed.
But you challenged me!
Yes, to a duel for the crown!
Enter the Pandora
Queen contest...
The winner of our
battle will be determined
by the votes received!
If you're not up for it,
you can always say no,
but that would mean
admitting defeat
and I would be the
victor of the duel.
But that's ridiculous!
Fine.
I will accept...!
Your challenge!
Wait... Are you sure
you want to do this?
No matter what form
a battle may take...
I will never admit defeat!
I'll be looking forward to it!
And just so you know,...
you'll need more than
big jugs to beat me!
Jugs?
And now coming to the stage
is entry number seven:
The Angel of Binding...
...second-year Ganessa Roland!
Just call me "queen"!
The Pandora Queen...
It suits me well.
Yeah...! Miss Ganessa
is number one!
Entry number eight,
the Releaser of Chastity,
third-year Miyabi Kannazuki!
Come and get it.
Hey... what's up,
you don't look so good.
I know I said I would,
but the truth is that
I don't think I can do this...
It's all so humiliating!
Oh-kay... Well, you have
already entered the contest.
Satellizer...?
Are you taking part
in this event as well?
What on Earth are you wearing?
It's an homage to the
clothing of my homeland...
Do you like what
you are seeing?!
It's... very flattering...
I guess.
Entry number eleven:...
The Pulsating Stomach
Flesh, third-year...
Maruki Tone!
A battle to become
Pandora Queen?
That's the idea.
What's this...?
Admitting defeat before
our duel's even begun?
I do not think that I will
be defeated by you either.
She'll be a tough one too!
Great...! It's so adorable
that you think you can win!
Entry number thirteen:
The Architect of Evil,
third-year Attia Simmons!
You go girl!
She is hot!
Lesson for the day:
A woman's appeal doesn't rest
solely on the size of her bust.
Learn it well, boys.
Whoa...!
She's getting a pretty
good response from the crowd.
Oh... it is my turn
to go up on stage!
Satellizer.
Any honors that
are won by a Pandora
are honors shared by her
partner, would you not agree?
Just think it over...
If you look at things like that,
even difficult
challenges become easier.
Now coming to the stage
is entry number fourteen:
the yet to be nicknamed
mysterious transfer student,
second-year Rana Linchen!
I believe it is right
to show compassion
even to someone who is my rival.
You'll be going up next...
so you need to get
ready now, please.
Are you leaving?
I'm going to see
this thing through.
You know you don't have to
do this if you don't want to.
I realize that...
This isn't something I want.
But I have to go
out there... for you.
What do you mean... "for me"?
Let's head to the stage...
You're up now.
My actions aren't just a
reflection of me, not anymore.
I'm doing this for us.
Up next, entry number fifteen.
Wait...! What's this...?
It's the Untouchable Queen...
That's right...
Give it up for second-year
Satellizer el Bridget!
What did he say?!
I'm seeing it,
I just can't believe the
Untouchable Queen is doing it!
Oh, my...
Now I think
I've seen everything.
That is strange...
Up until now, she's
never even attended any
of the social events
we've held here at school.
It's because of
Kazuya Aoi, of course.
Sister Margaret!
I believe that Satellizer
has found herself
an excellent partner.
She's frozen in
place out there...
She doesn't have a chance
against Attia
standing still like that...
She's gonna have problems
with the crowd soon, too.
It didn't even occur to me what
I was going to do out here...!
Now what?!
She is... incredible.
Yeah... and she looks
so innocent up there.
The Untouchable Queen
who's normally
so merciless and terrifying,
now appears to be so
demure and fragile...!
She's a tour de force!
Yeah!
How humiliating!
Satellizer.
You were great out there.
Now our final entry
for the evening...!
Last year's Pandora
Queen... third-year...
The Executor of Ingenious
Schemes, Elizabeth Mably!
It looks like I couldn't
find Mr. Right after all.
Do not worry about it.
You will have plenty of chances.
Yes... there will
be many opportunities
to challenge you after tonight.
So are you excited...?
About the results?
I was terrible... I just stood
there doing nothing at all.
Not only were you
courageous out there,
but you did it all for me...
I thought it was... inspiring.
Uhm, Kazuya... I just...
Yes?
Well, I thought
that if you'd like...
I mean...
What is it?
I... I thought maybe
we could formally--
It's finally time to
announce the results...!
We'll start with our
fifth place winner!
She is...
Miyabi Kannazuki!
Oh come on,
don't act so surprised!
Uhm, I've just received
some information...
There was an
irregularity in the voting.
Therefore, Miss Miyabi
will be disqualified...
...which means fifth place...
is awarded to Ganessa Roland!
You did it...! I told you
you'd place, didn't I?
I hate to say it,
but this is far from how
I pictured things going.
In fourth place: Rana Linchen!
Kazuya...! I am in the top five!
Congratulations.
Third place with one hundred
twenty-seven votes:
Third-year, Attia Simmons!
Attia ended up
in third place...?
So that means if you end up
getting first or second,
she'll have to admit
that you beat her!
You were great out
there, Miss Attia.
It's merely adequate.
Taking second place
with a hundred ninety-eight
votes: third-year...
Elizabeth Mably!
So Elizabeth didn't
take first place again...?
Then who won the crown?
Who could have stood a
chance against Elizabeth...?
Can you think of anyone?
No... Nobody.
And now... your new Queen...
With five hundred
sixty-eight votes:
second-year,
Satellizer el Bridget!
What?!
Me?
Wow... Neat.
What a surprise...
Don't worry, there's still
something I can do about this!
Hey! Where are you going?
Congratulations Satellizer!
This is so exciting...!
I see that Kazuya
is proud of you too!
I could accept defeat
from anyone but you!
Man... I never expected
the Untouchable Queen
to become the Pandora Queen!
You're sure you
want to use this?
Of course... This was
part of the visual theme
we decided on for
this year's prom...
Elizabeth had prepared
this dress herself.
Miss Elizabeth did?
Unfortunately,
she never anticipated
that victory would slip
from her grasp and
so we must all adapt...
That's why it's so important
to her that the new queen
be presented with it.
Well, in that case...
Stop...! Enough talk...!
Elizabeth wants
the queen to wear this
so that's what's going to
happen, is that understood?!
Yes... We understand.
Please, come this way.
Huh...? Wait... What now?
We have to hurry
so you can change into
your coronation dress!
My what?
The time has come...!
It's my honor to present
this year's Pandora Queen!
This outfit's disgraceful...!
It was hard enough to let people
see me in the dress I had on!
Did you have a
hand with that outfit?
I wanted to give her
something special...
It's a novelty dress
for couples.
It's a what?
Watch... The fabric
reacts to body heat...
...and then...
Woah... Hey!
It... can't be!
Hey, what's going on...?!
What's happening
to her clothing?
I... don't know!
The color fades and the
dress becomes transparent!
We finally taught that
impudent little girl
a lesson she won't soon forget!
Why would she
even have something
like that in the first place?
She's got a lot of
unresolved issues...
...that's my guess.
Kazuya, please help me!
Here, take my hand... C'mon!
Right, thanks.
Even the toughest among
us has a soft side.
She is the top ranked third-year
student here at East Genetics.
Her name is Cathy Lockharte.
Next time:
"Godspeed of the East."