[OHARA] Beginning today, I ask
for the sincere cooperation
of all Original Pandora to
ensure the program's success.
[gasps and whispers]
[OHARA]
This is the Mark IV.
They went ahead and
made another one?
It is comprised of
self-replicating nanomachines
and is installed
with data collected
from the Original Pandora.
Original Pandora data?
[OHARA] We will begin with its
distribution to the E-Pandora.
When the Mark IV
goes into effect,
their stigmata
will be activated,
raising their abilities to
a level that is comparable
to the Original Pandora.
[FEMALE CROWD] Ooh!
[murmuring]
[ROXANNE]
About the Mark IV.
If they already had
it up their sleeve,
why wasn't it used
for the mock battles?
That might've prevented 'em
from being so one-sided.
[splash]
[ROXANNE coughs]
[CHIFFON]
Speaking of the Mark IV.
I thought Chevalier
hadn't approved it.
Not yet, anyway.
[ROXANNE] Huh?
[CATHY]
It is weird.
Even if our data was collected
during our physicals,
wouldn't it most likely
still take a lot of time
to install the information?
Hey there! If it's not
the Godspeed of the East.
[ELIZABETH]
Think about it.
Grafting stigmata onto normal
girls is painful enough.
[CHIFFON, ROXANNE, and CATHY]
Huh?
But they're taking
things further
by activating the stigmata
with nanomachines.
And that means...
...before the E-Pandora
are even accustomed
to the artificial stigmata,
they're going to increase
their abilities to our level.
How long before their
bodies break down?
That's a good
question, Mably.
There's definitely
something fishy
with this E-Pandora business.
[CHARLES] Quit being
so paranoid about stuff
you have no say in, Zombie Girl.
Who the hell said that?
My name's "Roxanne
the Immortal,"
so get it right, bitch! Uh?
[ROXANNE] If it isn't
the Young Tempest Phoenix
and the Maverick of Walpurgis!
You know that
as a Pandora,
it is our duty to obey
orders without question.
You'd better not forget that.
How cute!
We should call you:
the Young Tempest Kiss-Ass!
[ROXANNE laughs]
[CHARLES sighs]
Hopefully you can understand
where I'm coming from.
Well, Miss Unparalleled Monster?
Yo Monster, are you
even listening?
[CHIFFON sighs]
[CHIFFON] You girls
are so heartless.
I don't know why you insist
on calling me a monster.
[CHIFFON]
Believe it or not.
I happen to think that
I'm kind of pretty!
[GIRLS] Uh?
Heh. Talk about
changing the subject!
Totally!
Aahh!
What do you think you're doing?
Yeah, these are
pretty impressive.
I mean, seriously,
at least double D's, right?
None of your
business creep!
We definitely won't be short on
entertainment with this bunch!
Yeah, but Don't let
the fun times fool you,
they're also going
to have your back
if things get hairy in battle.
Might as well try
and get along!
Roger that, A-cup!
Keep drinkin' your milk, okay?
Ugh! Zip it,
you stupid zombie!
[ROXANNE] Heh.
Flat-chest has got
a good point, guys.
[GIRLS] Uh?
[ROXANNE] We can't question
our bosses' orders,
what with the fate of mankind
resting on our shoulders.
And we've basically
already given up any shot
at a normal life.
Not the easiest decision,
considering we're all hotties.
Poor boys, missin' out on
all this youthful perkiness
and bona fide sexy for
the good of the world.
[GIRLS laugh]
[ROXANNE] Whatever.
I guess we're all kinda victims,
one way or another.
Damn, life can suck sometimes.
[CHIFFON] I wonder.
The Original Pandora data
that's being installed.
Whose do you think it is?
[MALE AIDE]
Amelia Evans is waiting.
She wanted to speak with you.
[OHARA] Chevalier has already
ordered use of the Mark IV.
We can't backtrack now.
Oh, That's not
why I'm here.
There's actually
something else on my mind
I was hoping to ask you.
[OHARA] All right then,
out with it.
About the
presentation earlier.
Is the Mark IV an upgraded
version of the Mark III?
[OHARA sighs]
[OHARA] Yes.
But I don't understand!
The Mark III was a failure!
[AMELIA groans]
[OHARA] It was, and
I'm reminded of that fact
every time I look at your hair.
But unlike the Mark III,
the Mark IV was developed
with the application
of the Original Pandora's
data in mind.
It boasts far greater
stability without bearing
any risk of side effects.
The Mark IV is head and
shoulders above its predecessor.
So you're sure...
that it'll be okay?
It doesn't matter!
[AMELIA gasps]
[OHARA]
Whether it's okay or not...
...isn't for you to decide!
Surely you knew what
you were getting into.
The contract that you
signed says it all.
You will obey any orders
regarding the E-Pandora project!
Don't play dumb and act
like you don't know the truth.
Your life no longer
belongs to you.
Understand?
You can't be serious.
We don't even have the right
to prevent our own deaths?
[OHARA]
That's correct.
Even if the Mark IV were to
kill one or two E-Pandora...
...it's all for the
sake of mankind.
I understand that, Doctor.
I just don't want to see
any of my friends die.
You think I would let you
girls throw your lives away?
Jina and Rattle were worried,
but they'll be glad to
know that we're all safe!
I want to thank you for taking
the time to explain everything.
[footsteps]
[door opens]
[AMELIA]
And doctor!
[OHARA] Mm?
[AMELIA]
The E-Pandora Project.
I promise we will
make it a success!
[OHARA sighs]
[OHARA] Stop!
We have to take out her
internal stigmata at once!
[MALE AIDE] But doctor, they've
already been activated!
Trying to remove them now
would be life threatening!
It's too risky,
we'll end up killing her!
Shut up and do it now!
Hurry! I'm not going
to let her die!
Aahhh!
[AMELIA] We trust you
with our lives, Dr. Ohara.
Please don't let us down.
[RANA and SATELLIZER
breathe heavily]
[RANA] Satellizer.
Tying with me...
is an impressive feat!
I am... equally
impressed by you.
In what manner should
we compete next?
Perhaps who falls
asleep the fastest?
[RATTLE grunts]
Oh! I apologize
for my clumsiness!
Hey! What is the big idea?
Do not eat that!
Throw it away and get a new one!
[RATTLE whimpers]
[RANA] Eh?
[JINA] Did you
just laugh at her?
Don't play dumb,
answer my question!
[RANA] Oh, sorry, I did
not mean to insult you.
A spoiled brat like you
would never understand.
Stop that.
A mere E-Pandora should not
go around picking fights.
You insulted my friend, and
now you wanna start with me?
[RANA] What?!
[AMELIA]
Stop it, Jina.
You know that Rattle
became an E-Pandora
so she would never have to
worry about starving again.
So why can't you
just let her eat?
[SATELLIZER sighs]
[SATELLIZER] Let's go.
[RANA] Ah! Hey,
what are you doing?
Release me right now,
I can handle my own conflicts!
Eating is more important
to her than it is to you,
so just leave her alone.
What are you talking about,
I was not being a bother!
And why would she eat that,
it fell on the floor!
[JINA] Hold it!
[JINA]
Do you pity us?
[SATELLIZER]
That wasn't my intention.
[RATTLE] It's not a big deal,
Jina, really, I'm fine!
[JINA] Be quiet!
I apologize for my
friend's rudeness.
I know that you're upset,
but I'd like to avoid
a fight if possible.
And why's that?
E-Pandora are still
no match for us yet.
[JINA gasps]
She is right!
You cannot beat
Original Pandora!
[SATELLIZER]
Quiet, you.
[RANA] Ah! Hey, you
are pulling too hard!
The straps are
digging into me!
Ouch! Let go! Now my
boobs are exposed!
[JINA] Damn it!
It's okay.
[AMELIA] Jina!
What's up Amelia,
is something wrong?
[AMELIA] I just heard
that you volunteered
to be given the Mark IV!
It's not that big a deal.
Why're you so worked up?
Why am I worked up?
This is the Mark IV
we're talking about!
There's no guarantee
you'll even survive!
[JINA]
Let go of me!
You were gonna go behind our
backs to try and volunteer
yourself again, weren't you?
[AMELIA gasps]
Just like you did
with the Mark III!
I hate how you're
always trying to bear
everyone else's
burdens for them!
We're in this together!
You already died
once for us.
I won't let you do it again!
However, thanks to
your experience,
the Mark III tests went
back to the drawing board
and no one else had to endure
the pain that you did.
Stop worrying, Amelia.
This time, it's my
turn to step up.
[AMELIA gasps]
I plan on surviving
through my contract,
then going back to
living a normal life.
Isn't that what we all want?
[RATTLE] Mm-hm.
[JINA] Besides, you've
got that kid brother
who's waiting for you
back home, right?
[AMELIA] Uh!
I just thought maybe...
...it'd be better if...
[JINA] Can it.
I'm gonna get so strong that
even you won't compare with me!
[JINA]
Please, Dr. Ohara!
I'll make the
arrangements.
[JINA] Ah! Thank you
so much, doctor!
No way.
Oh. Is that girl
the Original Pandora
you'll be using for
the Mark IV project?
Yes, the data
belongs to her.
[JINA gasps]
In fact,
I'm gonna be so good
that even the Originals
won't be able to beat me!
Heh.
Why?
This game is nothing
like doing sit-ups!
Guess I'd better start
heading back to my room.
Good game!
[RANA giggles]
There is no need to
be in such a hurry.
The night is still young
enough for us to have fun.
Actually, I think lights-out
is about to happen.
[RANA] Come now Kazuya, we have
plenty of time for indecency!
Just imagine
when it gets dark!
[KAZUYA]
Don't touch me there!
Hey, take your hand off!
[JINA] I volunteered for
the Mark IV experiment.
[SATELLIZER] Why are
you telling me this?
[JINA] Because the Original
Pandora data that's being used
in the Mark IV is
none other than yours.
Thank you for that.
[SATELLIZER] What?
But I didn't have anything
to do with their decision!
[JINA] That doesn't
really matter.
I'm gonna defeat you
using your own strength.
So I hope there aren't
any hard feelings. Heh.
[SATELLIZER] Uh?!
What makes you think
it's gonna be that easy?
[JINA] I'll see you
at the mock battle.
[ELIZABETH]
The mock battle.
[SATELLIZER] Uh.
I was originally planning
to volunteer for it.
[ELIZABETH chuckles]
[KAZUYA] What do you
think that E-Pandora
wanted to see Satellizer for?
I think Kazuya should
spend more time
thinking of things to do to me!
Let us get started! Whee!
[KAZUYA]
Stop it, Rana!
[RANA] Oh Kazuya, I hope you
are ready for our baptism!
[door opens]
[KAZUYA gasps]
[MALE AIDE] Artificial Stigmata
numbers stabilized.
The Mark IV is ready
to be administered.
[JINA] It's time
to make me strong.
As strong as Satellizer!
Check vital signs.
[MALE AIDE]
They're all green.
Perfect.
Commence Mark VI administration.
[MALE AIDE]
Commencing administration.
[JINA] Aahh!
[MALE AIDE] Mark IV
administration complete.
[MALE STAFF 3A] Artificial
Stigmata activity increasing.
Thirty, fifty, ninety.
[FEMALE STAFF 3A] Synapse
signalization currently normal.
[MALE STAFF 3B]
Micro-machinery Receptor
activation rate increasing.
Thirty, forty, fifty...
[FEMALE STAFF 3A]
Rapid increase occurring!
One-hundred five!
Three-hundred six!
It's still rising!
[CROWD cheers]
Now Volt weapon deploy!
[SATELLIZER gasps]
She actually did it!
Not too shabby.
Jina!
Ah! All right!
Volt weapon deploy.
Aaahh!
[SATELLIZER]
Acceleration!
Whoa she's got
some sharp moves.
[JINA yells]
[FEMALE NEWSCASTER]
Today, Chevalier revealed
the initial results of
its E-Pandora Project.
The project had previously
been veiled in secrecy.
The E-Pandora has power
that is comparable
to an Original Pandora.
She possesses advanced
skills and is capable
of producing a Volt Weapon.
In response, leading experts
have expressed optimism,
stating that they
now have high hopes
for the promising
E-Pandora Project.
[MALE STAFF 3A] Response
to the demonstration
has largely been positive.
Best of all, we now have public
support for the E-Pandora.
[SPENCER] We'll show off the
second and third successes
in a similar fashion.
[SPENCER] Hm?
How is the subject?
The unusual Stigmata activity
has not stopped progressing.
It's even eating away
at her body's tissues.
[SPENCER]
That is to be expected.
[MALE STAFF] Uh?
[SPENCER] However.
You need to keep her
alive for the time being.
Yes. By any means necessary.
[alarm sounds]
[OHARA]
Is she conscious?
[MALE STAFF 3A] Yes.
And more than likely
she's aware that she's...
She's changing
into a Nova.
What a terrible fate.
I'm sorry, Jina.
But there was never
any chance of success.
I'm sorry.
[RATTLE]
Um, Amelia?
Do you think Jina's doing okay?
It's been three days.
The doctor said that she would
be fine, but the procedure
is pretty draining so she's
probably in recovery right now.
You're right, Dr. Ohara
would let us know
if anything was wrong.
Yeah! So quit
worrying about Jina.
She'll be out of
there in no time!
[RATTLE] Mm.
[MALE AIDE] I'm afraid we've
tried everything possible.
[MALE AIDE] It's only a matter
of time until she dies.
Hey, ya did it!
Congrats Jina!
You have no idea
how proud we are!
[JINA] See them....
[AMELIA and RATTLE laugh]
[JINA]
I want to see them!
[alarm sounds]
Doctor, her vitals are
racing out of control!
How is that possible?
What's the cause?
[MALE AIDE]
I don't know!
Jina, no!
[SATELLIZER gasps]
[alarm sounds]
Hey! What was
that loud noise?
[loud thud]
[RATTLE and AMELIA]
Aahhh!
[AMELIA gasps]
[RATTLE whimpers]
[AMELIA] No, don't
tell me you're...
[SPENCER] You fools!
If you let it get outside,
this entire operation is over!
Do whatever it takes to
stop it, you hear me?
[MALE STAFF 3A] But what
exactly should we do?
Are you asking me to
tell you how to do your job,
you imbecile?
Use the Pandora!
[MALE STAFF 3A] But sir!
This could put
all of us at risk!
[SPENCER] Do you have
any better ideas?
It is imperative that
you stop this thing!
Send only those Pandora
that can get the job done.
Do it now!
[FEMALE ANNOUNCEMENT]
The aforementioned Pandora
and their Limiters are requested
for emergency mobilization.
Proceed to designated
positions immediately.
All other Pandora and
Limiters are to remain
in their quarters on
standby. I repeat.
This is not a drill.
I repeat. This is not a drill.
[AMELIA] Jina.
[AMELIA] If something
happens to me during
the next round
of experiments...
[ELIZABETH] I won't waste my
time talking to you anymore.
Why don't you just go
outside and cool down?
[SATELLIZER]
Next time. "Mate."