[KAZUYA gasps]
[HOLLY yells]
[LUIS gasps]
[LUIS] What are
you doing, Satella?
Move!
[KAZUYA] No matter what
scars you've left on her.
And no matter what pain
she carries because of you.
I respect her for the person
that she's become!
Yes! I love her
and I always will!
No, Luis.
You dare defy me for
this piece of crap?
[SATELLIZER]
Yes, I do.
Kazuya is more than my Limiter.
He showed me how to live again!
Thanks to you, I avoided
people for years.
I wouldn't let anyone get close.
But Kazuya taught me to trust.
He brought me out of my shell.
He means everything to me!
I'll protect Kazuya against
anything that threatens him.
I'll defend him.
Even if it kills me!
[LUIS laughs]
[LUIS] That's one of
the most ridiculous things
I've ever heard!
Stop being an idiot
or I'll make sure
Father won't listen to
what you have to say.
Now. Be a good little toy and
do as you're told, Satella.
You don't have to do
what he tells you.
There's the big sister I know.
The one who obeys my every whim.
I'll go easy on you
for disobeying me
but Kazuya's gotta pay
for his disrespect.
[SATELLIZER gasps]
[LUIS]
Are you kidding?
You don't stand a snowball's
chance in Hell against Holly.
I told you, she's one of
my academy's most powerful!
And I told you
something, Luis.
I will protect Kazuya against
anything that threatens him!
That includes her!
[LUIS grunts]
I can handle this.
[LUIS]
Just punish her.
[HOLLY] Right.
[HOLLY] Aaahh!
[HOLLY] I tried to tell myself
I was imagining things!
Aaahh!
But I knew, even though
I refused to admit it!
I knew.
There has always been someone
else in Luis' life. You!
[HOLLY]
What is that?
[LUIS gasps]
Oh. Uh...
It's nothing important.
Just sort of a good luck charm.
Who's that girl?
She your
girlfriend?
[LUIS]
No, just my half-sister.
Luis told me how much
you mean to him.
He's obsessed with you!
Come on!
I knew I had a rival!
But I never would have guessed
she'd turn out to be
Luis' own half-sister!
If it weren't for you,
he'd love me!
[LUIS] Why? Why does it
have to be this way?
Why does Satellizer
have to be my sister?
[LUIS sobs]
It's all right.
You can have me. Okay?
[HOLLY] Aahh!
No, it is not okay!
But why, Luis?
[HOLLY whimpers]
Ahh!
[LUIS] I dunno! 'Cause you're
just another tramp?
I'm the eldest son of
the El Bridget family!
You really think I could have
feelings for someone like you?
You're nothing more than a
temporary plaything to me!
And I might add, an incredibly
poor substitute for my sister!
[HOLLY cries]
[LUIS]
What's the matter?
I thought you just said
I could have you.
If that's the case
then keep serving
your master the way
you always have.
Even though you'll never be
as satisfying as she is.
Do you know how bad
it felt being told
that I'd never
measure up to you?
I've been living a lie
this entire time.
His eyes might have been on me.
But his mind and his heart were
always on you, "Big Sister!"
Tell me!
Why does it always
have to be you?
Can't it be me for once?
[LUIS] I didn't tell you
to talk her to death.
[HOLLY] Eh?
[HOLLY gasps]
[LUIS] You're really
starting to annoy me.
You don't honestly think you can
beat Holly in a fight, do you?
Would you like
to bet on it?
[LUIS] I can only say you're
being ridiculous so many times.
But sure, why not?
I don't think you have
any hope of winning.
But, if by chance you do
manage to defeat Holly,
I'll speak to Father for you.
She vanished!
[SATELLIZER] A non-interval
Double Acceleration!
Nice try!
But I saw it!
[HOLLY] Aahhh!
[SATELLIZER]
How'd she get behind me?
[LUIS] Bet you didn't
see that coming!
Switching from a Double
to a Triple Acceleration
like that is something Holly
mastered some time ago.
That's why it looked like
she changed places.
I'm impressed.
I have to admit,
you've got an advantage
over me with that move.
Even so...
I won't back down!
[SATELLIZER yells]
No... Sattelizer.
Foolish toy.
[SATELLIZER groans]
[KAZUYA]
You were hurt...
...protecting me.
[LUIS] I did warn
you about this.
You've seen what
Holly can do
so why not stop this nonsense?
Perhaps I'll be merciful and
forget that anything
ever happened.
I've always done
what you said.
I was your toy.
You were the master
I feared and obeyed.
The old me would've
said "Yes, master."
But. The new me says "Never!"
[KAZUYA] Sattelizer,
you have to stop!
[SATELLIZER] No.
Because I've got
you, Kazuya.
[KAZUYA gasps]
Together we can
achieve anything.
You've shown me that I can be
a lot more than Luis' puppet.
Did you hear that,
little brother?
As of today, I won't let you
have any more control over me!
Let Holly do her worst!
There's no way we can lose!
Yeah! We can't afford to!
You know I've got your back!
Let's do this!
We've wasted enough
time already!
Let's take 'em down and get back
to what brought us here!
What brought us here...
[inaudible]
[SATELLIZER] Exactly.
The E-Pandora.
[SATELLIZER] I have to stop
those horrible experiments.
I need my father's
help get the truth out.
Elizabeth tried.
I have to pick up
where she left off.
She must have come
close for Chevalier
to cook up that scandal
involving her family.
[lightning strikes]
People's lives
are at stake.
I refuse to surrender to anyone!
[HOLLY gasps]
Those are!
The wings of light that appeared
in her fight with Cathy!
Wait a minute, is that
Stigmata light?
Don't worry, Holly,
it's all just for show!
Teach her a lesson and pluck out
those ridiculous wings
along with her Stigmata!
Aahh!
Is that a Tempest Turn?
No, more like an Acceleration!
[SATELLIZER yells]
[LUIS] Watch out!
Holly, Ereinbar Set!
Freezing area!
[LUIS] You're still
my marionette!
And I'll be the one who is
pulling your strings forever!
Not anymore, Luis!
[LUIS] Stop trying
to fool yourself,
you'll never be
able to escape me!
[HOLLY yells]
How the hell was
she able to do that?
I said I had your back!
[SATELLIZER gasps]
[KAZUYA]
Let's keep it up!
I promise I'll always
be by your side!
Kazuya.
Come on, get real!
You two don't have
an Ereinbar Set!
There's no way
you can win!
And I refuse to lose to my
father's bastard daughter!
Kill her!
[HOLLY] Ah!
[SATELLIZER yells]
A-Aaahh!
Are you okay?
No, this isn't possible.
People lose to me.
It's never the other way around!
How could this happen?
I'm the eldest son of
the El Bridget family!
Not some commoner.
And you. Satella.
I don't believe it.
I thought you wouldn't
let anyone touch you.
Well. Besides me anyway.
I mean, after all...
...you're the Untouchable
Queen, right?
I'm not any more, Luis.
Not since Kazuya showed
me I didn't have to be.
[YOUNG LUIS] Satella.
There's no place in
this house for you.
You're all alone.
But I'll protect you. I promise.
[YOUNG SATELLIZER cries]
[YOUNG LUIS] I will
never leave you alone.
That's right, Satella.
All you have to do is be
my marionette forever.
You'll have to do everything
I tell you to do.
If you don't, I'll make sure
you and your mother are
kicked out of this house!
[YOUNG LUIS sobs]
[chains rattle]
I get it, Satella.
You're not the
scared little girl
who's all alone and crying
in the dark anymore.
Are you?
You no longer need
me at your side.
Now I'm the one
who's all alone.
I can't blame you.
Not after the way
I've treated you.
I can never atone for that.
[HOLLY gasps]
[SATELLIZER gasps]
[KAZUYA gasps]
[LUIS] I'm not alone.
Holly's always been by my side.
[LUIS coughs]
[LUIS] Holly?
She'll be okay.
She must really care for you.
Satellizer. Thank you.
[birds chirp]
[KAZUYA] So, your father's plane
is landing in a few hours?
[SATELLIZER] Uh-huh.
[phone rings]
[KAZUYA]
It's from Alaska.
Um hello?
This is Kazuya.
Hey, Rana.
It feels like ages since
I have heard your voice!
Running off with Satellizer
is without a doubt
the cruelest thing
you have ever done!
Why must you torment me so?
Would you hurry?
That call will show up
in the phone logs
if it lasts over a minute!
[RANA] Things are dire.
We need you to return.
There has been an
incident with Elizabeth.
What? Wait,
is Elizabeth okay?
[SATELLIZER gasps]
[ding]
[indistinct PLANE ANNOUNCEMENT]
[HOWARD] Really?
So Satellizer's
in Bali right now?
Yes, she is.
Violet called to
tell us of her arrival.
[HOWARD] Hmm...
[OLIVIA] Apparently,
she's in quite a hurry
and has to leave
before our flight lands.
[HOWARD] Satella.
I do hope you're well,
my daughter.
I've missed you.
This jet will get you
back to Alaska.
And as for our Father.
I'll talk to him.
I'll give him your message.
It'll be the first thing I do
once he arrives home.
Well, so long. Big Sis.
Satellizer.
It took a lot of courage
to do what you did.
So thank you.
[SATELLIZER exhales sharply]
[HOLLY]
Are you sure about this?
[LUIS]
I already told you.
I want to atone
for what I've done.
[HOLLY cries]
[OHARA] The next Nova Clash
isn't very far off now.
And when it happens.
It won't be the E-Pandora
who save the world.
[AMELIA] Please let
me volunteer...
[JULIA] Elimination phase
commencing, now.
[ROXANNE]
I'm beginning to wonder
if they really are the enemy.
[SATELLIZER]
Next time: "Rebellion."