Go in peace, child.
May the goddess Kunlun
be ever at your side
to guide and protect you.
Look thou, Rana,
and find he who shall
guide your destiny,
the young man to
whom you are fated...
Now arise!
Yes... Patriarch.
This is your standard Nova.
As you already know,
when they materialize here
from the dimension
of their origin,
all living things
within a certain range
are forcibly restrained.
In other words... their
appearance causes a Freezing.
And that is when a Limiter
must play his part...
It is his duty to neutralize
the Nova's Freezing area,
and create a space within which
his Pandora can kill her foe.
"Causes a Freezing." Hm...
Casting an omnidirectional
Freezing is impossible...!
That little unbaptized freak has
the same abilities as a Nova?!
Huh?
How'd he do it...?
Wait, what...?!
You don't know how?!
Uh... yeah... No clue.
So that's your answer?
Not a clue...?!
I'm sorry, but
that's just weird...
You've never been baptized
and you cast a Freezing
outta nowhere like that?!
That is kinda weird, huh,
Satellizer was in trouble
and the Freezing happened
before I knew what was going on.
I know it doesn't make sense.
You weren't thinking about it...
Okay. Well...?
What'd "Satellizer"
have to say about it?
Nothing yet...
I haven't really seen
her since the fight.
Huh...?!
You put your life on the line
to save her butt that night...
And you haven't even gotten
a lousy "Thank you"?!
Hey, it's fine.
See...?
What've we been telling you?
That Satellizer is nothing
but bad news, my friend...
She's hot, I'm not
gonna lie to you...
Hey, I totally understand
how you could get sucked
in by a beauty like that.
Thanks, but what
are you talking about?
Roses are beautiful, too--
doesn't mean the
thorns don't hurt.
Uh-huh--and she's got
the biggest thorns of all...
One little prick
and you're done for.
Uh...!
What a surprise.
Good afternoon, ma'am...!
It's funny, we were just
talking about your beauty,
and now you're, here!
Yeah...! Yeah,
we certainly were!
All the boys in our class are
absolutely smitten with you!
It's embarrassing
how they carry on!
So Kazuya... listen.
Ma'am?
I wish to speak
with you in private...
Follow me.
Yeah...! Okay!
Uh... what was that all about?
It's called being whipped.
So, uh... why're we here?
I knew it...
Huh?
You're all right.
I had a feeling you were...
Even when... you touch me...
...it doesn't make me feel bad.
That's never happened
before... Never.
M-Me, too...!
Ever since the very
first moment I looked at you,
well, it feels like
I've been dreaming.
No... I keep thinking you're...!
It's just that I've never
known this feeling before...
When I try explaining
it, the words--
You can cast
Freezing areas, right?
You can, can't you.
Even without the Ereinbar Set.
Yeah... I guess
you could say that...
But I've tried it a couple
of times since then
and I haven't had any luck...
Starting to think it
was a one-time thing.
I've decided.
Decided what?
I'll do it... I hereby agree to
make you my Limiter, Kazuya!
Are... you sure you wanna?
Yes... But I can't
baptize you, okay...?
As long as you don't
mind that... then I...
Of course I don't mind!
Thank you, Kazuya...
You're very kind.
Thank you.
This is the West
Genetics Academy...?
Oh... wow, how
wondrous this place is!
Here, so far from home...
Kunlun shall surely
lead me to him...!
The man who is my destiny!
It may not be official,
but it's enough for me.
Burgers are okay, right?
Oh... sure.
Hold on...
She bought all those for me?
There's no way
I can eat all this...
You're not eating.
Thank you for the food...!
I just hope you brought enough.
Kazuya... well...
are you busy tonight?
Tonight...?
Well, not really, no.
Then... Would you like to...
I'm listening.
Never mind.
Oh.
Damn it!
Huh?
I would be honored,
if you would come up
to my room tonight!
You... want me to
come to your room?
Exactly! You'll do it, right?
Uh... yes, ma'am...
I'll do whatever you want.
It's neat that she invited
me to her room, but...
I don't get why she
seemed so nervous about it?
This campus is enormous...
How long have
I been walking now...?
Huh...? Who's that girl...?
And what is that outfit about?
At long last I have
discovered somebody else!
Uh... congrats...?
Oh, you're a
transfer student...?
Guess that's why she's
not in a school uniform...
Your campus is
impossibly vast...!
I was afraid I would be doomed
to wander its paths for
the remainder of my days.
I don't think
it's as big as that.
You'll find the
principal in there.
Yes! Many thanks
for guiding my way!
You are very kind!
You truly are a
gentleman, are you not?
Just helping out...
It was nothing--really.
How the goddess smiles
upon me this day...!
All thanks be to Kunlun
for granting me such kismet!
Farewell!
Who's Kunlun...?
Crap...! It's almost time
for me to meet Satellizer!
What are you worked up about?
Huh?
Whaaat...?!
The Untouchable Queen
actually said that?!
She wants to pair up
without a proper baptism?!
Mhmm.
Woah...!
Without the Stigmata,
how are you even a pair?
There won't be any proof!
Why doesn't she
want to make it official?
If you ask me, I think she's
just using you for your power!
I'm with Hiiragi on this one.
If Satellizer doesn't
want to do right by you,
you might as well turn her down.
You deserve better than that.
You've got it all wrong, guys!
She even asked me
up to her room--
that's where I'm headed now.
You're going to her room?!
For real?
You actually got a room invite?!
From her?!
What's the big deal?
When a Pandora
chooses her Limiter,
she invites him to her room!
It's like tradition.
The guys certainly approve.
Why is that?
You know...!
If you're gonna work as a team,
you have to get nice
and close to your Pandora.
The "big sisters"
have to make sure
the "little brothers'"
needs are taken care of.
I still remember my first
room invite with Ganessa...
kinda...
I might have gotten
liquored up first...
I was out like a
light until morning.
Wow.
Was it good for her?
Official or not,
at least the Untouchable Queen
gave you a room invite.
That's something, right?
Still... without a baptism...
You know it's bad
news--right, Kazuya?
C'mon, you guys...
I would be honored,
if you would come up
to my room tonight!
Satellizer doesn't
seem like she'd be
into that kind of thing,
tradition or not.
Is she forcing
herself to do this?
Maybe he'd like
this one on me...
Unless... this one
is more his style...
I'd like you to consider
selecting me to be your Limiter.
Think things over for a sec.
Are you sure you wanna do this?
You can still back out.
Nothing's set in stone.
I'm going inside...
I'm sure it'll be just fine...!
See ya later!
You should watch where
you're going, first-year.
You're right...
I'll be more
careful next time...
Please excuse me...
Hold on.
Um, I'm kinda in a hurry.
Hey, you're that kid...
Yeah, you're the
weird little boy
who keeps begging to
be Satellizer's Limiter.
Ah--so you're the new guy.
Well... Not much to look at...
So... Am I to believe
that "Her Highness"
has consented to
be paired with you?
Oh, please no!
Say "no"--say "no"!
Yeah... I guess...
Wrong answer...!
That's just marvelous,
isn't it, girls?
Y'know what...?
Since we're all here...
How about we help you
celebrate your big night?
Huh?
You must be tired
after your trip.
Sleep well tonight,
you've a busy day tomorrow.
And if there's anything
about life at this school
you don't understand, please
don't hesitate to ask me.
Okay, Rana?
Thank you!
That is very kind, Miss Chiffon!
As principal of West Genetics,
please allow me to extend
my thanks to your patriarch...
His decision to send you
to us was a generous
one, Rana Linchen...
You are welcome here.
Stop picking on him!
What did you say?
The three of you ganging
up on him isn't very fair.
Well, look at that...
An underclassman mouthing
off to her seniors...
I'm just saying, he's
not looking for trouble!
Au contraire--he brought
this upon himself!.
Isn't that right!
Do I know you...? Who are you?
Really...?
You're saying you don't
know who the three of us are?
No. Why?
Audrey Duval, at your service...
But most know me as
"The Slice-and-Dice Maiden."
My name is Aika Takeuchi, aka...
"Intoxicating Bondage."
I'm "Twin Fang" Tris McKenzie...
Forget my name
and I'll kick your ass...
Are we clear on that?
I know these girls...
they all lost to Satellizer
in the most recent Carnival.
Wait, so then
that's why you're--?
Why are you doing this?!
Isn't it obvious...?
You kids could use
some... discipline!
Sometimes you
first-years get too big
for your britches and
forget your proper place...
We consider it our
duty to remind you.
Fine, I'm reminded!
I think I'll play
with you first...
You really shouldn't
take too long.
I don't care if you
are all upperclassmen...!
If you're looking for a fight,
I'd be more than
happy to oblige!
You little bitch...!
What are you doing,
are you crazy?
Just walk away!
Too late for that, kid...
You've got to pay
for your disrespect.
That's right...
Discipline's not gonna cut it...
I think we better
just kill this one!
Nice try, but
you're way too slow!
Say goodbye...
you mouthy little brat!
Hiiragi... Hiiragi...?
Hiiragiiiiiiii!
I'm... gonna go get a teacher.
You're not going
anywhere, blondie...
I really don't
think that snitching
is very manly behavior, do you?
You're a naughty
little boy, aren't you...?
I guess I'm gonna
have to break you in.
It's for your own good.
I think "discipline"
is the preferred term.
Yeah... But in the end
the result is the same.
As long as I can make
you bleed a little bit,
that's good enough for me!
This is most strange...!
No matter how long I search,
the girls' dormitory
continues to elude me...!
How are you
doing down there...?!
Tell me how much you enjoy it
and maybe I'll
leave you something!
Oh dear...
It seems like Takeuchi has
slid into her cruel ways again.
Leave him alone...!
As if...
Who gave you permission
to talk, first-year?
Honestly...
They're just letting anyone in.
Let my friends go.
Let them go...!
Try not to do too much permanent
damage to 'em, ladies...
What the hell...?
What are you
mumbling about, kid?
Let them go or you'll regret it!
Oh!
You are quite the
edifice, girls' dormitory!
Let them go...?
You have got a lot of
nerve for a first-year.
Do you really think
you can treat my friends
like that and
get away with it...?
I'm not letting you...
hurt them... anymore!
Kunlun's Tears are vibrating...!
This sensation--!
No... I can't move anything!
Why did they all just stop...?
Oh no, don't tell me...!
Not again...
Get that chain...
...off of my friend...!
Frozen with no set...
Who are you?!
Are you telling me...
...that the Untouchable
Queen is gonna make
this first-year her Limiter?
This strong of a boy paired
with a Pandora like her...?
I'm sorry... but I don't
like the sound of that!
No...! Don't do it!
Quiet down, I'm not killing him,
all I'm going to do is
carve him out a little memento,
that way the next time he
thinks of sticking his nose in
where it doesn't belong
and Freezing his betters,
he'll remember the
consequences and mind...
...his own business!
Hey, where the hell
did she come from?!
Do pardon the question, miss,
but what are your
intentions towards him?
What the...?!
Why do you talk like that?!
Know this: I will not let you
harm one hair upon his head.
Kunlun's holy tears spoke to me
the moment I laid eyes upon him.
The boy is mine, and I am his.
What kind of
new age crap is that?!
Damn, she's strong!
Hey, you...!
Can't they count
where you're from?!
You're up against
three of us, ya know!
You don't actually think
you can beat us, do you?!
You little--!
You want tears,
I'll give 'em to ya!
We can fight more,
if it pleases you.
She's... unreal!
Yeah... This is the one...
It'll be perfect.
It's about time...!
How long did you intend
to keep me waiting?
Uh... sorry...
I know it's
pretty late, ma'am...
So how is he?!
He's been out since it happened.
They moved him to the infirmary.
Oh-- and she's the
one who saved him.
Is he awake?!
So you are a
schoolmate of Kazuya's...?
They are saying he'll be fine...
Perhaps you would
like to wait with me,
my hope is that
he will be allowed
to have visitors quite soon.
Wait with you...?
You mean to say...
you're a student?
Well, I have not yet been
enrolled into your academy...
if that is what you mean.
But I will be soon.
I transfer into West Genetics
first thing in the morning...
My name is Rana Linchen, miss...
I am most happy to meet you!
You're a transfer?
Oh, Rana--hey... you, uh,
mind if I borrow you for a sec?
Sec?
Hiiragi said she wants to
thank you for saving her, too.
I am waiting to see Kazuya...!
This comes first, okay?
Just trust me on this...!
Um...!
Goodness... Can I help you?
Kazuya Aoi... How is he?
Kazuya...? You sound
worried about him.
No--not at all...
Well, maybe a little.
That boy... I tried to tell him
that he's pushing
his body way too hard.
It's nothing fatal.
He's just exhausted.
Not that you're
worried, of course.
Well? Get in there already.
You came to see him, right...?
He needs someone by his side.
Oh, Kazuya...
So... you're a
transfer student, huh?
Our patriarch ordered
me to come here
that I may discover
the man of my destiny.
Wait--"the man of your destiny"?
Truly...!
That is the fate of all women
who carry Kunlun's
Tears upon them.
Behold--the blessed
tears of the goddess.
Stigmata?!
Yeah, but--six?!
I kinda figured as much,
with how crazy strong you are.
Hey, Rana...
You were a Pandora back in
your hometown, weren't you?
Pandora...?
I do not know that word.
You speak the truth?!
Kunlun has wept on a great
many girls at this school,
from what you say!
This is serendipitous!
Wait, so... by man of destiny,
you mean a Limiter, don't you?
You'll get one, no problem--
there are boys
all over the place!
But I have...
I found my man of destiny
my very first day here!
He is Kazuya Aoi...
Fate has doubtless
brought us together.
He is my soul mate--he
and none other.
That might not be
such a good idea.
Yeah, he's... off the market.
What do you mean by that?
Well... Satellizer,
that girl you just met...?
She called dibs on him...
So you're too late.
So... The Untouchable Queen
has finally surrendered
to the touch of another person.
And we still don't know
what other sorts of tricks
that first-year boy might have
hidden up his sleeve, do we?
That's all well and good,
but I'm more interested
in that foreign girl
who seems to have
appeared out of thin air.
Suffice to say... things
are getting interesting.
After I finish beating you...
That's right--dance,
little puppets.
...you'll never interfere
with us again.
After I finish beating you,
you will remove
yourself from Kazuya!
Next time: "Machination."