Freezing area!
Now deploying Volt weapon.
Halcyon...! Double Acceleration!
Triple Acceleration!
Quadruple Acceleration!
So that's her...
the Godspeed of the East...
Yes... She is the top
ranked third-year student
here at East Genetics.
Her name is Cathy Lockharte.
Satellizer!
Are you daydreaming
about your time
with Kazuya at the big dance?
What makes you think
I would spend all my time
fantasizing about him?!
I can take that
as a "yes," then?
I have more important
things to think about...
...and besides, Kazuya
isn't even here right now.
Wow, this is a real honor...!
Thank you so much for
inviting me to East Genetics!
No, thank you...
I'm sure you're busy,
so I'm grateful that you
took the time to visit us.
There's no need to
be so polite with me--
even if I'm a guest,
I'm still your junior!
I suppose so...
Miss Lockharte here is
one of the chosen Pandora...
After the Eighth Nova Clash,
the Stigmata of Kazuha Aoi
were deemed as "Sacreds"
and given to select
Pandora like Cathy.
So that means you have
my sister's Stigmata?
As soon as I heard that
Kazuha's younger brother
had enrolled at West Genetics,
I did everything I could to
arrange for you to come here...
I thought I should at
least pay my respects.
Thank you, thank
you so very much.
Don't thank me...!
I didn't have anything
to do with it...
So you're number one
in the whole school...
I suppose I don't
look like much, do I?
I didn't mean it that way...!
Your Quadruple Acceleration
was really something else!
I didn't even know Pandora
could move that fast...!
And you beat two Nova at once!
Even so, that would never
happen in an actual fight.
Surprised...?
In all our encounters... we've
only seen one Nova at a time.
Right... I almost forgot...
But it doesn't
matter... because...
...I plan on retiring
after this year, anyway.
I thought someone like you
would join Chevalier for sure...
That's what all the good
Pandora do their fourth year
so they can work with the
anti-Nova reserve forces, right?
I may seem strong but, I don't
think I'm suited to that life...
I'd like to pass my Sacreds
on to someone more deserving.
Why would you say that?
There's... something else
I want to do with myself.
Something else?
I actually want
to be a novelist.
I'm sorry, what did you say?
I just said I want
to be a novelist.
Say again?
I want to be a novelist, okay?!
I hope you don't think
that's disrespectful,
I know that as a Pandora
it's incredibly important
for me to fight
against the Nova...
But even so...
Since I was little... I've
always wanted to be a writer.
That must sound
pretty strange...
I wouldn't blame
you if you laughed...
Actually, I think
that's wonderful.
Besides, if you're
half as good at writing
as you are at fighting Nova,
it'd be a crime if I didn't
get to read your work!
Thank you!
Are you sure about this...?
I can't change your mind, can I?
No... I'm sorry, Miss Milena...
I'm afraid not.
Who'da guessed...?
She wants to be a novelist...
It's a real shame.
She has a special
sort of talent,
the same kind that I saw in
your sister, to be honest.
I'm not certain
how much she told you
about her time as a Pandora,
but she was truly
a hero among heroes.
With 20 Stigmata in her body,
she was able to make
even the most abstract
of skills a reality.
After your sister's fatal
encounter with the Nova,
a number of her Sacreds were
passed on to Miss Lockharte,
who was found to have a very
rare 90% compatibility rate.
In all the Genetics
branches in the world,
not one other Pandora
has shown the same
degree of compatibility...
That is why I say it's a shame.
Please forgive my
disappointment...
We thought you would be the hero
that would lead the Pandora
in their next battle...
You could have
led the Chevalier.
I'm not worthy of such praise.
My father is a
politician, you know.
He's the only reason I entered
this school in the first place.
Of course I couldn't
let him down
by dropping out
before I graduated,
so I've given it my best
these past three years.
But that's all...
I don't want to go on.
I know my responsibility...
I'm still a Pandora...
and I'm not against
fighting the Nova...
Even after I graduate,
I'll do everything I can to
protect my friends and family.
But continuing
on to Chevalier...
being praised as a
hero and a leader...
that's more frightening
to me than anything.
It's frightening?
I may seem strong...
...but I don't have
the same strength
that a true Pandora has.
An unyielding will to face
any threat without fear...
...and a heart
as resolute as steel
with absolute faith in herself
and her mission alike...
I believe that these are
a Pandora's true strengths.
You're saying you
aren't like that?
No. I'm not.
I'm not a true Pandora.
I learned that lesson myself...
Or rather, someone who used
to go to school
here taught it to me.
Who was it?
You must remember the
fight I got into with her,
so I'm surprised
you even have to ask.
A year ago, when Brooks Leevon
was permanently injured...
...is that what you mean?
Yes.
Are you insane--
What are you doing?!
Satellizer el Bridget.
A true Pandora...
That day...
I learned the real
meaning of strength...
...and I learned who
I really was... a coward.
So that's why...
These Sacreds...
If Kazuha had 20 of them,
does that mean anyone
besides Cathy received
them after she died?
But Cathy, you have
six Sacreds, just like she does!
She's the same as you!
Satellizer has them, too?!
Yes... although an exam taken
before she transferred showed
that her compatibility
rate was under 5%.
Maybe that's why I mistook her
for my sister when
I first came to the school...
She has Kazuha's Stigmata...
Aoi...
Uh... yes?
I have heard...
...that you were intending to
become Satellizer's Limiter?
Yes ma'am, I was...!
I mean, I am.
I haven't received the baptism
yet, but I'm still her partner.
Is that a fact...?
To be honest, after the
incident at East Genetics,
I did worry about her,
but I think you two
will be a good pair.
What really
happened back then...?
All I heard is that
some student wanted
to be her Limiter and
she hurt him really bad.
But there's more
to the story, right?
Yes...
Although she did
indeed injure the boy,
he later admitted that
she only became violent
after he tried to force
her to partner with him.
Oh... so that's it...
Actually he was quite fortunate
that Cathy Lockharte
was there to help him...
If she hadn't shown
up when she did,
he might have
been hurt even more.
I didn't know she
was part of this, too...
Satellizer's family is in
charge of the El Corporation...
Some people say
they're the reason
she got the Sacreds
in the first place...
...but I don't see
why you'd fear her.
Right from the start,
the difference in our
power was clear...
She didn't stand a chance.
And yet, even when it seemed
like the fight was over,
she didn't show a
single sign of giving up.
Just the opposite, in fact...
She came at me again and again,
regardless of how many
times I struck her down.
This was someone who
refused to be defeated,
no matter how much the odds
were stacked against her.
Our reason for fighting and
what we carried in our hearts...
...was clearly different.
When I saw what a true
Pandora was made of,
I realized how
weak I really was.
It was insane...
I kept fighting until
another third-year showed up
and we were finally
able to stop her.
I may've "won"...
But I lost all my
nerve in that fight.
Even if I do have these Sacreds,
I know someone like me isn't
fit to lead other Pandora!
I had no idea.
Under East Genetic's
jurisdiction?
Correct...
The dimensional interference
that we picked up
recently ended up
being the Nova after all.
Level 1 Alert! Level 1 Alert...!
This is message for all Pandora
and Limiters
currently on campus!
Pandora, equip Volt Textures
and prepare Volt
weapons immediately.
Limiters, change
into battle uniforms
and assemble in the
auditorium...
Volt Texture: Equip
This is message for all Pandora
and Limiters
currently on campus!
Pandora, equip Volt Textures
and prepare Volt
weapons immediately.
Limiters, change
into battle uniforms
and assemble in
the auditorium...
This is live footage.
I've never seen
anything like this...
As I'm sure you're aware,
we are under attack
from Type S Nova.
There are four of them.
Four Nova?
Target 1 has breached
the defensive line.
Civilian evacuation is
proceeding on time...
Currently at 95% complete.
We will intercept the targets in
one minute and thirty seconds.
All units were destroyed.
Should have known...
Can't even slow them down.
Those poor soldiers
never stood a chance.
Milena...
Understood.
We have received our orders.
General Headquarters
has stated that all students
must move out to serve as
backup Limiters and Pandora.
Kazuya!
Did you hear?
Yeah.
Four S-Class Nova at once...?!
This is totally nuts!
You don't think
they'll come here, do you?
I'd like to see 'em try!
Give us a chance,
and I bet Gannessa and I can
take out a Nova or two...!
They won't know what
hit 'em when we show up!
Now hold on a sec...
Even if she's strong,
Ganessa's a second year...
I know this is bad,
but there's no way they'd
send underclassmen out there.
But we don't know that...!
I heard that East doesn't have
enough Pandora to keep up...
Even second and third
years who aren't assigned
to Chevalier were ordered
to help with the fight.
Even the ones who aren't
moving onto their 4th year?
Well, it's an emergency,
what else can they do?
Then that means...
Cathy has to fight, too...
We will reach the mission
area in 15 minutes...
All personnel,
prepare for descent.
Chevalier Platoons 3, 7,
and 8 have completed deployment
and are nearing the target.
Full-force assault
will begin in 180 seconds.
Target 1 is
continuing its advance.
Decoys are now in place.
Strikers are now in place.
Alright, looks like the
Finishers are in place as well.
Operation commencing
in 10 seconds...
Five... Four...
Three... Two... One...
All right, decoys, spread out!
Keep it busy so the Strikers
can launch their attack!
Freezing!
Strikers! This is your chance!
It's time to move in!
Expose the core!
Finishers, get to that
core and destroy it!
Quadruple acceleration!
We're counting on you,
Cathy Lockharte!
She's almost there!
Time to finish this!
Cathy, are you okay?
Did it time its attack
to intercept me...?
It knew my quadruple
acceleration was coming!
Filthy monster...
Decoys, time for round two...!
Distract the Nova one more time!
We're picking up high
energy readings from Target 1!
It can't be...
Since when can Nova
fire beams like that?
This isn't anything
like their last attack.
It was foolish of us
to think we'd seen the
limit of their strength,
and this is the price we
must pay for our ignorance.
Incoming message from GHQ...
West has been
ordered to mobilize.
So it's true.
The personnel at East
isn't enough to stop them...
That's why they're making
our fourth-years move out?
Well, there's four
Nova this time...
That's never happened before.
I know I probably sound
like a coward saying this,
but I sure am glad
I'm a third-year right now.
Yeah, it's scary.
I do not understand this...
Why does everyone look
so scared and anxious...?
They are all speaking
in whispered tones!
At least tell me what
you are so angry about!
She's just frustrated.
Misses Student council
president and Vice President!
Frustrated at her
inability to do anything
in this time of emergency.
Emergency...? Please explain.
I'm sorry, wait...
Do you mean to tell me
that you have no idea
what's going on right now?
I haven't a clue.
So... what are you gonna do
if they order us to move out?
What do you mean?
Like, what about Satellizer...?
Would the two of you pair up
and fight with everyone else?
I mean... you haven't received
your baptism yet, right?
Oh, I forgot...
You don't need an Ereinbar
set like the other Limiters,
so you could team up with just
about anyone you wanted,
couldn't you?
It doesn't matter.
Satella is the
only partner I need.
So of course
I would fight with her.
She's really special to me.
Special, huh?
But... what do you mean?
I realized it the first day
I transferred here...
When I saw Satella...
she looked just like my sister.
Like the hero of the
eighth Nova clash...?
Kazuha Aoi, right?
Is that why you hugged
her when you first met?
But now I finally understand.
It's because she has
six Sacreds on her back...
The exact same
Stigmata my sister had!
So hold on... you don't
want to become her Limiter
because you two are friends
or anything like that?
It's just because
she's like your sister?
I don't know.
Maybe subconsciously...
My eyes...! I can't see!
Somebody help me!
Get the medics out here!
What do you mean how many?
All of them!
Target 1 is performing
another unknown attack.
What's going on?!
They appear... to be fusing!
It's penetrating at
the point of contact
and combining with
her Stigmata framework!
Her Volt Texture
is being neutralized!
Cathy... hold on!
I have to get away... Now!
Is that you, Miss?
Quadruple Acceleration!
It's no use...
What's happening to me...
It's taking control of my body!
No!! Cathy!
It's because she has
six Sacreds on her back...
The exact same
Stigmata my sister had!
So hold on... you don't
want to become her Limiter
because you two are
friends or anything like that?
It's just because
she's like your sister?
Giving birth to the
Pandora meant planting
the Nova's framework
upon humanity's back.
I'm not just some
substitute for your sister!
Those are the Pandora
that the Nova absorbed.
Next time: "NOVA Form."