[alarm sounds]
[FEMALE ANNOUNCEMENT]
The aforementioned Pandora
and their Limiters are requested
for emergency mobilization.
I repeat.
The aforementioned...
[RANA]
Satellizer, halt!
You must not do this;
we were given specific
orders to remain here!
Something's not
right about this.
[FEMALE ANNOUNCEMENT] I repeat.
This is not a drill.
[JINA] Aaaaahhh!
All right,
keep it up!
C'mon, you can do
this Jina, take her out!
[JINA] Aaahh!
[gasps]
[buzzer]
[FEMALE ANNOUNCEMENT]
Match over.
[JINA gasps]
[JINA] Dr. Ohara!
When Amelia fought her you
let the fight continue!
I deserve that chance too!
This mock battle has a different
purpose than that one did.
You have proved conclusively
that the Mark IV
can strengthen the E-Pandora,
and that's a win.
Wouldn't you agree, Jina?
Yeah. Sure.
She's right, this is
a massive discovery!
Because of you, we know
the Mark IV has the ability
to make us stronger.
[SATELLIZER] Her signs of Nova
transformation are gone.
[applause]
Well...
She's a lot stronger than
she was. Don't you think?
Thank you so much.
I'm glad it's your data
that's giving me strength.
It was so amazing.
I could feel what
you were fighting for
every step of the way.
The things that
matter most.
The people you hold dear.
Your desires. I felt it all.
[SATELLIZER]
I'm not special.
[JINA] Eh?
I think all the
Pandora are that way.
[JINA] I see.
Well done E-Pandora!
Let us henceforth protect
the world arm in arm!
The truth is, for most of my
life I always hated the world.
But. Now I finally feel
I can learn to like it.
[SATELLIZER] Hm.
I'm a real E-Pandora.
And I'm proud!
[alarm sounds]
[FEMALE ANNOUNCEMENT]
This is not a drill.
I repeat: this is not a drill.
[RATTLE whimpers]
Help me. Amelia.
[AMELIA gasps]
[AMELIA] Jina!
Tell me: what's
happening to her?
[ELIZABETH]
She's changing into a Nova!
It must be due to the Mark IV!
[ELIZABETH] What the hell
do they think they're doing
in this laboratory?
[JINA] Aaaaahhh!
[SATELLIZER gasps]
No! Jina!
[ELIZABETH]
Stay out of this.
[SATELLIZER gasps]
[ELIZABETH] You were ordered
to remain on standby.
Your help is not required here.
She told you she doesn't
need your help, so back off!
[AMELIA gasps]
[ELIZABETH gasps]
[JINA yells]
[ELIZABETH] She's so
fast I can't keep up.
A Tempest turn and
an Acceleration?
This is goodbye.
Please, you can't do this!
Jina's still conscious,
I know it!
[ELIZABETH gasps]
Where did she go?
[JINA yells]
[SATELLIZER] Behind you!
[JINA grunts]
[AMELIA yells]
[gasps]
[AMELIA winces]
Don't worry. I will always
protect you, Jina.
No matter what happens.
A-Amelia, I...
The Mark IV is...
The Mark IV, it's a--
[OHARA]
I'm sorry, Jina.
But there was never
any chance of success.
The Mark IV is
a what? Go on.
It's no good.
Mark IV is a sham.
[AMELIA gasps]
[ELIZABETH]
What are you saying?
No, it can't be.
[JINA yells]
[CHARLES] Heh.
[ELIZABETH]
Where did you come from?
You okay?
[ELIZABETH]
I'm fine.
[ELIZABETH winces]
[CHARLES]
Yeah, you look it.
That's what you get
for not mastering
Accelerations or Tempests
and then trying to use
them both at the same time.
Miss Charles,
what's going on?
The answer's obvious.
This girl's clearly a monster.
Now watch and learn.
[French music plays]
[JINA yells]
[CHARLES] Looks like someone
wants to play a little game
of catch me if you can.
[CHARLES]
Typhon Tempest!
Eight different images!
[SATELLIZER] I didn't
even know a human could
do something like that!
[ELIZABETH] It takes real rhythm
to control eight copies.
But to maintain them.
I guess Jina's not the only
monster in this room.
I'm just glad this
one is on our side.
[CHARLES] Aaaahhh!
[CHARLES yells]
[CHARLES]
Aahh! Huh?
[ELIZABETH] How was
she able to adapt to
Charles' attack
pattern so quickly?
[CHARLES] My Typhon Tempest
didn't faze her at all.
[JINA yells]
[ELIZABETH] This is the
power of a Nova form
drawn out by the Mark IV.
No! Stop!
[ELIZABETH] Stay back.
Take another step, and I'll
see you court-martialed.
[CHARLES] I should know better
than to walk into a fight
without my favorite song on.
[French music stops]
[Classical music plays]
[CHARLES]
Volt Weapon: deploy!
Vibrato Hell!
[CHARLES]
Haah!
[CHARLES] Typhon Tempest!
Moonlight Sonata Version, go!
[CHARLES yells]
[CHARLES] Heh.
[ELIZABETH] Incredible.
How is she able to carry out
her orders with so
little hesitation?
[JINA yells]
[CHARLES] Aaahhh!
[AMELIA] No, Charles, don't!
Please, don't kill her!
[squelches]
[Classical music plays]
Well, I guess it's over now.
Behind you!
[CHARLES] If it weren't for her,
I wouldn't be alive right now.
[AMELIA screams]
Why did you kill her?
Huh? Why?
You didn't have to do that!
You could have let Jina live!
She was still conscious.
You could've stopped her
without killing her.
[AMELIA sobs]
Jina. She was still there.
And you killed her!
It's so sad.
[RATTLE sobs]
[AMELIA]
Goodbye, Jina.
[JINA] The Mark IV.
It's no good. It's a sham.
[AMELIA] A sham.
If that's true then
you fell for the lie
and it swallowed you whole.
I promise you, Jina.
There will be a reckoning.
[group cries]
[OHARA]
What's going on here?
I don't recall giving you girls
permission to start a fire.
I thought you
might be involved
when I got word of
this little gathering.
What is this, a funeral?
[AMELIA] Yeah.
She was one of our own,
it's only right we do this.
Do you know what Jina
told me before she died?
She said the Mark IV is a sham.
[RATTLE] A-Amelia.
[AMELIA] You knew this
was going to happen
from the very beginning,
didn't you?
So I guess...
...that we're just some
kind of Guinea pigs
for your twisted experiments?
[OHARA] Even if Chevalier does
think of you in those terms,
you can take comfort in
the fact that the sacrifices
you make are for the
betterment of humankind.
However, this doesn't mean the
Mark IV experiments are over.
Now put out that fire and
return to your quarters.
You really think
that we'll obey?
[OHARA] Of course you will.
You don't have a choice.
[PANDORA 4A]
Guys, did ya hear what happened?
That powered up E-Pandora
turned into a Nova,
so they had to kill her.
[PANDORA 4B]
Yeah, that's crazy.
Sounds like the
Mark IV's a bad deal.
[PANDORA 4C] Good thing
we're real Pandora
and not some experiment.
[PANDORA 4A] I know.
[PANDORA 4B]
You want my opinion?
That's what regular people
get for trying to become
something they're not.
[RANA]
Greetings, Satellizer!
Perhaps you would be so
kind as to accompany me
to Kazuya's room!
Or conversely, I could
venture there on my own.
Heh! Perhaps I will wear this!
Imagine what a
scandal it would be!
Might I inquire as to
what is troubling you?
[SATELLIZER]
It's none of your business.
I know not what the precise
meaning of your abrupt exit is.
But if you mean to
ignore a direct order,
I fear trouble awaits you.
Greetings, Elizabeth.
You should listen
to your friend,
there is no point in
what you're doing.
And why is that exactly?
[ELIZABETH] Because I just
went to see Dr. Ohara myself
and she refused
to talk to me.
Satellizer.
I have to say, it doesn't
seem like your style
to stick your nose
where it doesn't belong.
[SATELLIZER]
The Original Pandora data
installed in the
Mark IV is mine,
so I'd say I'm well
within my rights.
[RANA] Huh?
An innocent person
transformed into a Nova
and was brutally killed because
that data was given to them.
I know you heard what she said.
Jina called Mark IV a big sham.
She truly made that claim?
It's just like
you told me.
A Pandora is a Pandora,
no matter what.
And honestly,
until I met Jina,
I thought you were
just saying that!
But she showed me you
had it right all along.
[JINA] The truth is,
for most of my life
I always hated the world.
But. Now I finally feel
I can learn to like it.
I'm a real E-Pandora.
And I'm proud!
[SATELLIZER]
But now she's dead.
She's gone forever.
[ELIZABETH] I see.
Somehow, you think this is your
fault, and you want to help.
Well, it isn't, and even
if it was your fault,
I would still tell
you to stay away.
[SATELLIZER] Why?
Because this is not
any of your business.
[SATELLIZER] Yeah?
Whose is it then?
[ELIZABETH]
I don't know.
Excuse me.
[ELIZABETH]
A bit chilly, isn't it?
[AMELIA]
Oh, Ms. Mably.
[ELIZABETH]
Ms. Mably's my mother.
I've told you this
before and I meant it:
you can call me Elizabeth.
For what it's worth,
I think it's a real shame
what happened to
Jina Purpleton.
[AMELIA]
With all due respect,
It's really none
of your concern.
Yeah, I guess you're right.
It's probably not.
So, are you planning
on moving forward?
I know that's not
really my business.
But that doesn't make
me any less curious.
[AMELIA] We don't exactly
have a choice in the matter.
At least that's what
our contracts say.
[AMELIA] I imagine this
is just the beginning
for the E-Pandora Project.
People like me will start
signing up by the dozens.
[AMELIA] And when one
experiment goes awry,
they'll just move
on to the next one.
They'll keep going forward
like nothing ever happened
in the first place.
But, I'm sure they can
only keep their failures
hidden away for so long.
At least my sacrifices might
prevent future E-Pandora
from falling victim
to these experiments.
[ELIZABETH] So what?
You're going to volunteer
for the next experiment
to protect a bunch of people
you've never even met?
What about protecting
yourself, Amelia?
[AMELIA] I hate
to do this to you.
But I have a favor to ask.
If something happens to me
during the next
round of experiments,
please go see my brother.
Will you?
If it comes to that,
please tell him we were friends
who fought side by side
for a good cause.
If you could tell
him I died bravely
fighting for the
principles I believed in
it would mean the world to me.
That's pretty awful
of me, isn't it?
I have no right to pretend
that you and I are friends.
Forget that I even asked.
You're probably right.
I suppose we don't know
each other well enough
to call each other
friends just yet.
[AMELIA sighs]
But I do respect you.
And I can honestly say you're
one of the few people here
I feel that way about.
[ELIZABETH] I'm proud to have
made your acquaintance, Amelia.
From the bottom of my heart.
Me, too.
Thanks, Ms. Mably.
[ELIZABETH]
I told you already...
I would like you to
call me Elizabeth.
[AMELIA cries]
[AMELIA] Thank you
so much, Elizabeth.
[ELIZABETH] Doesn't it
seem a bit suspicious?
Hm? What're you
talking about?
[ELIZABETH] The Mark IV.
Something was off about
it from the very start.
And now a person is dead.
I wonder if the Mark IV was
ever meant to succeed at all.
It seems the earlier
prototype, the Mark III,
had its fair share of
controversy as well.
[CHIFFON] Perhaps you should
keep your voice down.
Is it a lie?
The whole E-Pandora Project?
[CHIFFON] It's like
you always say.
We can talk ourselves
in circles all we want,
but at the end of the day,
there's nothing we can do.
[ELIZABETH]
That's not true.
[CHIFFON] Huh?
[ELIZABETH]
We can do something about it.
If we work together we
can come up with a plan.
I am proud to call myself
a member of Chevalier.
The things that
we do are entirely
for the preservation and
betterment of human kind.
If I ever let my
faith in that waver
the importance of the Pandora
would be lost as well.
Are you saying that
you're okay with this?
You're going to
ignore everything
that happened to Jina?
As Pandora, we have to.
It's our job to do
whatever it takes.
Sometimes that means people
get hurt in the process.
And that's just how it is.
Leave the politics
to the politicians.
[ELIZABETH] Well, then.
I guess I'll have to
involve my family.
What is it you would need
to involve your family for?
[ELIZABETH]
You were listening.
Well, never mind.
It's like I told you before:
stay out of it.
[SATELLIZER] Why won't
you let me help you?
You're asking your
family for help,
so why not ask the
same thing of me?
Obviously, you're willing to
sacrifice your pride because
you feel that there's
something important
you need to accomplish.
I think I can help
you make it happen.
[ELIZABETH] Is she talking
about reaching out
to the El Bridget family?
I don't like
repeating myself.
This isn't your concern,
so stay out of it.
[SATELLIZER]
Then I'll do it myself.
Oh yeah? Do what?
I'm only trying to help you.
Why won't you let me?
You need to learn your place!
[SATELLIZER yells]
[SATELLIZER] Why?
[ELIZABETH] I won't waste my
time talking to you anymore.
Why don't you just go
outside and cool down?
Outside?
[KAZUYA] What are you doing?
That's against the rules!
[ELIZABETH] If any harm
comes to me or my family...
[KAZUYA] We're supposed to be
flying back to West Genetics!
[LUIS] It's good
to see you, Sister.
[SATELLIZER] Next time,
"Noblesse Oblige."