If I asked nicely, could
I convince you to surrender?
You don't need to say anything--
I already know the answer.
Pleased to meet you,
I'm Ticy Phenyl...
Third year, rank 3,
the Silent Confidant.
And I'm Chiffon Fairchild...
Third year, rank 1...
"The Unparalleled Monster."
I'm going to die here, aren't I?
I'm still... alive...
Still breathing... over there...
little miss... rank two?
Ganessa, no!
Are you okay...?!
Answer me! Ganessa!
You can't die on me,
you gotta hold on...!
What were you thinking,
doing something like that?!
It... was my duty...
What?
I have to protect...
my comrades...
No... I have to protect
those weaker than me...
It's my duty... as a Pandora.
Just hold on a little
longer. It'll be fine.
Watch, I'll take you straight
to the recovery center...!
Pandora get injuries
like this all the time
and they patch them
right up no problem!
I'm sorry ma'am.
I shouldn't have picked
you up without asking.
Oh no, I got a little
dirt on your face...
You always try so hard
to stay clean and pretty, too,
I'm really screwing this up.
Let's try again, okay...?
If you didn't like
the piggyback maybe
we can do something else...
Oh! I know!
I'll carry you like a princess!
I know you don't mind that!
That's better, isn't it?
Tell me it's okay...!
One word is all
I need... anything...!
Just please talk to me!
"Why are you crying
so much, you fool?"...
"Stop wasting
time and carry me!"
Scold me like you always do--
I know I deserve it!
Please!
I'm sorry Arthur,
but it's over... she's...
Don't tell me she's dead...!
Ganessa wouldn't die so easy...!
She's much stronger
than that...!
She can't be dead!
This isn't the end,
you hear me?!
It's strange, you know...
I never wanted
to make friends...
For the longest time,
the only person I cared about
at this academy was me.
Then this happens...
I don't understand.
If I'm not supposed
to care about them,
then why do I feel so angry?!
Stigmata Activation
Rate 180... 200...
300... 400... Entering
abnormal activity levels.
She's switching to Nova
Mode of her own volition...
The same way that girl
did four years ago.
Quadruple Acceleration?!
There is no way she can
keep up with that speed!
She blocked it!
Amazing!
She held off
every single attack!
What is this?!
I've never seen
anything like it.
So this is your true strength...
Finally... it's all over now...
Please, kill me... end it...
Please... kill me...
No!!!
She's back to normal--she's
not a Nova anymore...!
The fight is over now...!
She's no different than you
Satella--you can't kill her!
Cathy has suffered
enough already!
It's not fair
for her to die here!
And I don't want to see
my partner take the life
of one of our allies...
of one of my friends!
Our ally...? Your friend...
Abnormal Stigmata
activity is causing
a dependency on Nova
attributes in the subject.
There's no turning back...
Stigmata Activation Rate:
200... 180... 120...
She couldn't be reducing those
Stigmata Levels on her own...
No. This is her
Limiter's doing, isn't it?
Satella... you're okay...
Ganessa!
Kazuya, quick, give me a hand!
Ganessa's still alive!
These are good tidings indeed!
I have to know...
Why did you stop...?
Even after I begged
you to kill me?
I did what I did for
the sake of my partner...
So he wouldn't lose hope.
Besides, if you're
half as good at writing
as you are at fighting Nova,
it'd be a crime if I didn't
get to read your work!
He taught me
something important.
What was it?
Because you showed me that...
...that when I'm with you...
I can protect the world
my sister fought to save!
He taught me what
I have to live for...
The goal that we must be willing
to sacrifice our
lives to protect.
Something to protect...
Maybe I've had the wrong
idea about this after all...
All finished here...?
Well that's a relief.
Thank you for the
hard work, Yujin.
My pleasure Miss Chiffon.
You were great, Abel!
Always happy to lend a hand!
All enemy Pandora who entered
the Ravensborne Nucleochade
have been eliminated
by our emergency team.
What about the Nova?
Only Target 1 remains,
but its core has
been badly damaged.
It should just be a matter
of time before it's defeated.
The last one... Let's do this!
Right...
It's gone!
Okay, so now what?
Target 1 has disappeared!
Make a sweep of the area, now!
Already underway!
Miss President...?
Is something wrong?
Control room...!
The enemy Pandora are--!
What now?!
Extra-dimensional
activity detected
in the vicinity of
the Holy Remains!
Nova detected and
transfer has been confirmed!
Put it on the monitor!
A Nova!
Confirmed: It's Target 1!
It must have acquired
the coordinates
through the stigmata it
attached to the Pandora.
Attention: This is a
message for all Pandora
inside the
Ravensborne Nucleochede.
The Nova must not advance...
Under no circumstances
can they be
allowed to reach
the Holy Remains.
You must protect them...
I beg of you.
Good timing!
So this thing is a Nova?
It always comes down
to a matter of brawn
over brains, doesn't it?
Well, we can't think
the Nova to death.
Save the chit-chat for
the after-party, girls.
I agree.
Okay Andrei... get
ready to back me up.
Of course, my lady.
Okay, team...
Let's give this our best!
Satella! What's wrong?!
Destroy it...! Kill me!
That Stigmata...
It looks just like Cathy's!
Stigmata have entered
abnormal activity range.
The Nova have recognized
the Pandora's abilities...
Now they're going to
use them to destroy us.
You have to fight it!
I... I cannot move!
What's going on?!
It can't be...
No mistaking it...
This is a Freezing!
It's Satellizer!
She's turning into a Nova...!
Target 1 is approaching
the holy remains...!
All Pandora remain
unable to act!
So in the end, all that we
can do is sit here and watch?!
I refuse to accept
defeat, even now.
Defeat?
Not yet... It's not over.
Pandora Mode, Activate!
What is this?
Pandora Mode, of course...
It allows us to keep moving,
even within a Freezing Area.
Well... this should
make things easier...
It's reversing our Pandora Mode!
They can do that?!
It sure looks like it.
The Freezing Area...
It's just too strong...!
What can we do?!
I don't know...
I've never seen this before!
Target One has reached
the holy remains!
You can't give up!
Help me...
Help me... Please...
Kazuya... I need you to help me!
I believe in you Satella,
I know you can do this...!
And not because of the Sacreds,
but because you never give up...
...because you're my partner!
Kazuya...! Kazuya!
I know you...
You're Kazuha... aren't you.
You must protect them...
The people that you hold dear
and all of their dreams as well.
They're your strength...
The hope carried
in your Stigmata.
On my back, I carry
the hopes and dreams
of the people I hold dear...
I must protect them,
no matter what.
This feeling of warmth...
It's an Ereinbar Set...
But he hasn't received
baptism, has he?
I never knew Kazuya
had power like this...
I feel so warm and fuzzy inside!
All right, team...
Let's finish this!
Target 1 has been
immobilized...!
They did it!
Seems it was no mistake
that she encountered that boy.
We should be grateful.
Miss Satella...
Kazuya... I spoke to your
sister before I woke up.
Thank you, Kazuha.
Watch out!
You're okay, right?
All thanks to you.
I'm glad you're back.
The Untouchable Queen
has a soft side, huh?
By the way, Miss Milena?
Hm?
I've been thinking it over
and I decided I want to
join the Chevalier reserves.
You... changed your mind?
Thanks to something
you said to me...
You made me realize what
we Pandora should live for.
But... Cathy, what about
your dreams to be a novelist?
Don't worry, I'll still
make that come true...
Besides... I made a promise.
Rana!
Now, it is time for us to go!
That's right, we
still need to stop by
and see Ganessa, don't we?
Yep!
Take my arm, Kazuya...
Ah, okay, okay...
Uh, excuse us, ma'am.
This is it.
Come in.
Hey, sorry we're... Oh!
Why are we not
entering the room?
Satella...!
You're visiting Ganessa, too?
I suppose...
I understand you're surprised...
I certainly am...
If this keeps up we might
even see snow in July!
I... just wanted...
to thank you.
Now, if you'll excuse me...
Come by my
room later, all right?
She really has changed.
We can scarcely call her
the Untouchable Queen now...
But she was long overdue
for an attitude adjustment.
Are you okay, ma'am?!
Of course!
I'll get it right this time...
You'll have your baptism.
Which one...? I can't decide...!
Kazuya! What a
pleasant surprise!
What are you doing
here at this hour?
Uh, well, Satella told
me to come by her room,
so here I am...
What should I do?
I have to wear something!
Satellizer, are you presentable?
Kazuya is here to see you.
Am I here too early?
So... hey... where
are your clothes?
I was just...
You were planning
to seduce Kazuya
with those lacy
undergarments, were you not?
My goodness, how shameless!
But I shall not be defeated!
Look Kazuya, I am even
more shameless than she!
What...?! I won't lose...!
Not to you... Not to anyone!
Ladies, could we
maybe... not do this?
It's as I feared.
This proves that the Stigmata
truly are a doubled-edged sword.
It is because they are
a double-edged sword
that they give birth to the
strength of our Pandora.
But Gengo...
I mean, Professor Aoi--
Good day, Sister Margaret...
This was but a trial...
Now it all begins.