[MALE PILOT 1A]
Chevalier Alaska Control.
This is Osprey
Double-Z Zero One.
Maintaining
flight level 9000.
[FEMALE AIR TRAFFIC CONTROLLER
1A] Osprey Double-Z Zero One.
[RANA]
The cold is unbearable.
Hold me. Please!
What are you doing?
Uh, you're really close.
[RANA] Perhaps proximity
will engender warmth!
[KAZUYA]
Oh no, that's okay.
I mean, I feel warm enough
'cause of my jacket.
But I bet it is cold
in that uniform.
[RANA] All the more
reason to embrace!
Shall we then?
[KAZUYA] Back off!
You're suffocating me!
[RANA] I must stave
off this frigidness.
If I don't snuggle up
next to you immediately,
I'm likely to turn
into a popsicle!
Here, feel for yourself!
[KAZUYA]
Hold on a second,
what exactly are you
making me touch?
[RANA]
Is it not obvious?
[KAZUYA]
Okay. Enough of that!
[RANA] I beg you, keep not the
warmth of your flesh from me.
But instead, enfold
your arms in mine,
so this winter chill
might go away!
[KAZUYA]
Let go of me!
[RANA] I see now
you will abandon me
to the despair of
my wintry fate.
Volt Textures do
have cold protection
and heat retention capabilities.
Oh, yes.
Why, of course.
Must have escaped my mind.
[beeping]
[MALE PILOT 1A] We're picking
up a distress signal.
Changing course now
and headed to site.
Distress Signal?
I wonder what that's all about.
I don't know.
Never mind that no one
has shared with us
the purpose of the
expedition to begin with.
[MALE PILOT 1A]
We're closing in,
the distress signal's coming
from right below us.
[MALE PILOT 1A] Snow's really
coming down out here,
we've got zero visibility.
[FEMALE AIR TRAFFIC CONTROLLER
1A] Osprey Double Z Zero One.
Proceed with caution.
[MALE AIR TRAFFIC CONTROLLER 1A]
Do not attempt to engage.
I repeat: until you have
visual confirmation,
do not attempt to engage.
[SATELLIZER gasps]
[MALE PILOT 1B] We have
a visual on a Nova Type S!
I don't understand,
what's a Nova doing
all the way out here?
This is Kazuya,
did you guys pick up
its dimensional vibrations
when it appeared?
[MALE PILOT 1A]
This blizzard is hell!
None of our equipment
is functioning properly!
[OHARA] Don't worry.
I've got this under control.
Is someone else
on this line?
About three kilometers
ahead of your location
is a Chevalier
petroleum storage base.
Your priority is
to stop the Type S
and defend the base
at all costs.
You're not serious, are you?
There's only two Pandora here!
[OHARA] Relax; reinforcements
are on the way.
[KAZUYA]
They'd better be.
[OHARA] If that location
is compromised,
the environmental impact
will be catastrophic.
The petroleum spills
will result in
widespread seawater
contamination.
You're the only ones who can
stop that from happening.
[KAZUYA gasps]
[MALE PILOT 1A]
The wind is way too choppy
to make a safe landing.
Once the hatch is open, commence
combat operations immediately.
Umm. Would someone
care to translate please?
When the hatch opens up,
we jump out and start fighting.
[RANA and KAZUYA] Huh?
Are you ready?
Do I have a choice?
Right. Let's go!
[MALE PILOT 1A]
Good luck down there.
Now what?
You tell me.
[RANA chuckles]
How'm I supposed to know?
[whirring]
The reinforcements
are here already?
[MALE COMM 1A] All units.
This is mission control.
Proceed to combat area.
Target is in sight. I repeat:
target is in sight.
[OHARA]
It's about to start.
[AMELIA] We'll be there
right away, Doctor.
What a tremendous success!
Yeah.
[RANA gasps]
They deployed
cruise missiles?
It's almost like
they're too prepared.
[OHARA] Now the
real show begins.
Pay attention, ladies.
[AMELIA]
That's her.
She's The Pandora who protected
West Genetics in Japan
during the infamous
Tenth Nova Clash.
Volt weapon. Deploy!
Volt weapon, deploy!
[MALE COMM 1A] Attention
Pandora ground team!
[SATELLIZER] It's too risky
to face that Nova head on.
[MALE COMM 1A]
Tracking marker enabled!
Warning: point five miles
to glacier terminus
from present location.
Pandora Ground Team.
Proceed with caution.
I'll draw the Nova
out into the open.
And once I do. Rana?
I will bury the evil
machine alive!
If anything goes haywire,
I've got your back!
[SATELLIZER] Right.
[SATELLIZER grunts]
Aaahh!
[MALE COMM 1A] A member
of the Pandora Ground Team
is currently in flight.
Identity confirmed.
It's Satellizer el Bridget,
the Untouchable Queen.
Scanning for Volt Texture index.
[RANA] Yah!
Sacred extremities
fist. Flame fang!
Compared to
other occasions,
this victory was
quite easy to achieve.
Way too easy,
if you ask me.
[KAZUYA]
You guys!
Hey!
There you are!
[KAZUYA gasps]
[SATELLIZER gasps]
Is that Chiffon Fairchild?
[rumbling]
And Elizabeth Mably
is here too.
You're not injured,
are you?
What are you doing here?
Hey, Andrei. Take good
care of him, will ya?
Whatever you say,
my lady.
[CHIFFON] Satellizer and Rana,
you're on decoy duty.
All right, I'll serve
as the striker.
Elizabeth, you're the Finisher.
Let's put an end to this thing!
[CHIFFON]
Yujin. Get ready!
You can always
count on me, ma'am!
Ereinbar Set!
[CHIFFON grunts]
This Nova, I should've known!
[JINA]
West Genetics' Pandora
are even stronger
than the rumors say.
[OHARA] Japan is Doctor
Gengo Aoi's native land.
And the remains
of Maria Lancelot
are still in the
Ravensbourne Nucleochede.
That's why so many
prestigious debutantes
from all over the world
have gathered there.
Prestigious debutantes, huh?
More like spoiled brats.
[ELIZABETH]
It's a bit strange.
[CHIFFON] So you
noticed too, Elizabeth?
[ELIZABETH] Yes.
[CHIFFON] Rumor has it,
they've been developing
these Nova dummies
here in Alaska.
[ELIZABETH] If you look
at this whole ordeal
as basically a test run,
it makes sense they would
be so overly prepared.
That's standard test procedure.
[SATELLIZER] So, you're saying
they went to all this trouble
to send us down here,
keep us completely in the dark,
and fake a distress call just
to involve us in an exercise?
Actually, Elizabeth
and I were told
this thing was related
to disaster relief.
[SATELLIZER sighs]
Whatever the reason,
this much is clear.
Somebody's trying to test us.
And my gut tells me this
was only the beginning.
Kindly avert your eyes!
[SATELLIZER]
Huh? Aah!
[CHIFFON chuckles]
[CHIFFON] You could always
use your Volt Texture
to cover yourself up, ya know?
[RANA]
Kazuya, are you in pain?
[KAZUYA] Huh?
[RANA] Miss Satellizer all but
accosted you, did she not?
[KAZUYA]
You're overreacting, Rana.
No, I am only concerned
for your well-being.
Besides, is it not my duty
given that you are my Limiter?
Wait a second, since when
is Kazuya your Limiter?
He's already mine!
I was under the impression
you have yet to hold
a baptism with Kazuya therefore
rendering your claim obsolete.
But--
She is conceited,
pious and quite prudish
when it comes to contact
of the physical variety.
As a result, I believe she
would be far more effective
in the role of a helper.
Ah! What?!
A helper? Get real!
Aah!
[CHIFFON giggles]
Will you please stop
acting like children?!
Yes, ma'am.
Seriously, this is no
time to joke around;
we're here to help
the E-Pandora Lab
by providing them with
critical info, remember?
[RANA] Yes, I suppose
you are correct.
Wait, what is an E-Pandora?
[SATELLIZER] E-Pandora are
artificial Pandora.
[FEMALE NEWSCASTER] As directly
evidenced in the recent
Tenth Nova Clash, these Nova
appearances are widespread,
becoming more and more frequent
with each new occurrence.
In an attempt
to counter this,
Chevalier General Command
has just announced
its adoption of a brand new
Pandora initiative.
Doctor Scarlet Ohara spearheads
this cutting edge effort
known as the E-Pandora Project.
Upon turning
eleven years old,
all girls are now required to
take a Pandora aptitude test
to determine their ability.
In the past, only
those girls who possess
a certain level of
Stigmata-compatibility
were allowed to live as Pandora.
Of course, those
who meet the standards
have always been free
to accept or decline
the offer to become Pandora.
However, there are those
girls who want to fight
but aren't allowed due to
incompatibility issues.
These girls will finally
have their chance.
Regardless of
previous standards,
the E-Pandora Project allows
ordinary, incompatible girls
to become Pandora by implanting
artificially created Stigmata.
[RANA] Trust in me Kazuya,
the taste is a Kunlun Harmony
of fragrant flavors
that bursts in your mouth!
The pasta place
makes this?
Yes!
I shall take you there soon so
you may see with your own eyes!
...persistently
opposed the project,
citing, among other things,
its unethical nature.
[FEMALE REPORTER]
Doctor Aoi! Can you tell us
how you really feel about
the E-Pandora Project?
Considering the project's
been given the green light,
I don't see how my personal
feelings are of any consequence.
[FEMALE NEWSCASTER]
But the real question remains:
if this project works,
can we actually call
these girls "Pandora"?
[KAZUYA] I wonder why
he's not speaking his mind.
[FEMALE NEWSCASTER]
Onto other news,
Seiga Heavy Industries
was the center...
[ELIZABETH] In my view,
artificial or not.
A Pandora's a Pandora,
plain and simple.
[ELIZABETH] I assume there
will be those who volunteer
to become E-Pandora
simply for the status
they'll be guaranteed
after their tour of duty.
But as it is now.
Less than two percent
of girls verified to be
Stigmata-compatible go on
to become Pandora anyway.
It's a dangerous occupation
and everyone knows it.
Countless Pandora
have lost their lives
fighting against the Nova.
Fact is, we need more help.
And given the circumstances.
I think it would be a mistake
to reject Pandora volunteers
strictly because they
happen to be the product
of some experiment.
Our ranks are thinning.
We have a worldwide
shortage of Pandora.
This may be the key to
solving that problem.
You really believe that?
Ah! It appears
we have arrived!
The laboratory is
straight ahead!
[KAZUYA] Looks like
this place used to be
some kind of industrial plant.
And the perfect location to
keep a secret covered-up,
don't you think?
[KAZUYA] Huh?
[CHIFFON] Don't mind me!
I'm just kidding!
[KAZUYA]
Yeah, thought so.
[KAZUYA chuckles]
[FEMALE OPERATOR 1A] Stigmata
memory area formatted.
Trigger setup complete.
Now idling in buffer mode.
[FEMALE OPERATOR 1B] Rewrite
system engaged and ready.
Quantization gate enabled.
[FEMALE OPERATOR 1C]
Texture installation system
ready for scan.
[FEMALE OPERATOR 1A]
Scan now.
[FEMALE OPERATOR 1D]
Once the scan is complete,
we will install Volt Texture
data into each of you.
[RANA] Did she say
"Volt Texture data"?
[ELIZABETH] It's probably
customized for this facility.
[CHIFFON] Feel that?
These cold protection and
heat retention capabilities
are way better than
the Genetics data.
[chattering]
[RANA]
Ah! My goodness, me!
It appears they are having
some sort of gathering!
[CHIFFON] Skilled Pandora
such as yourselves
have been called here
from Genetics facilities
all around the world
to collect data samples.
Pretty neat, dontcha' think?
Indeed it is! I feel
quite overwhelmed!
[SATELLIZER sighs]
[ROXANNE]
Chiffon! Hey! Heh, heh.
Long time no see!
I know! Not since
the World Carnival!
[ROXANNE] Yeah! When you kicked
my butt from here to next week!
[CHIFFON laughs]
Well, I suppose some proper
introductions are in order.
This is Roxanne Elipton.
She's an old friend of mine
from Genetics America, US.
Just call me Roxanne
the Immortal!
So, do you two
have names or what?
Am I truly to believe this
young lady cannot be killed?
[ROXANNE] Hmm...
[CHARLES]
Actually, she's a zombie.
What?
You're just as sassy
as ever, I see.
Who's that girl?
The infamous Charles Bonaparte
of Genetics France, LDT.
Also known as the
Young Tempest Phoenix.
[CATHY] Satellizer!
[SATELLIZER gasps]
[CATHY giggles]
[CATHY] I was hoping
I'd see you here!
Cathy Lockharte!
[RANA] Ah! It is her!
She is the Godspeed
of the East who did
mighty combat as the
lesbian nude cheetah!
[CATHY] Lesbian?
Oh, don't listen to her.
She's a bit on the slow side.
[CATHY yells]
Supple with a perfect mix
of firmness and bounciness;
if I were to make a guess
I would say at the smallest,
she's a D.
What are you,
like a boobologist?
This girl is the one
and only Julia Munberk.
Genetics Germany, Panzer.
Also known as the
Maverick of Walpurgis.
[PANDORA 1A] Guys, look!
It's the Fabulous Five!
[chattering]
Well, she's right.
They are nice.
[SATELLIZER]
What's the Fabulous Five?
[ELIZABETH]
You don't know?
Those four ladies,
along with Chiffon here
just happen to be the
five most highly ranking
third-year Genetics
members in the world.
Don't sell your talent
short, Elizabeth,
you're just behind
them in ranking.
[ELIZABETH]
For now at least.
I'll be fighting a
pretty tough opponent.
Holly Rose of
Genetics Britain, UK.
Speaking of,
I'm a bit surprised
she hasn't shown her face.
Yeah, it's not really like
her to be late to a party.
[FEMALE ANNOUNCEMENT]
Attention, all Pandora.
Please conduct your
Volt Texture equipping tests
in the designated fitting rooms.
Also, in the event you should
encounter any equipping errors,
please report them...
Volt Texture! Equip now!
Yep. Fits like a glove.
I don't know, I think
I like it better naked.
Oh well, Volt Texture
Equip, I suppose.
Sexy.
Much like you,
your undergarments
are lacking in taste.
Hey!
Satellizer! Have you changed
into your new garments yet?
It feels quite delightful!
[SATELLIZER yells]
Oh, suck it up,
first-year.
[RANA gasps]
[SATELLIZER]
There's no way I can wear this.
It's so short!
My name is Scarlet Ohara,
and I am the head of
the E-Pandora Project.
The purpose of this
initiative is quite simple.
But the benefits we will
gain are immeasurable.
Our goal is to
artificially produce
Stigmata-compatible
subjects.
In order to successfully
complete this endeavor,
I will need data from you,
the original Pandora.
This will be a game changer.
Thanks to the data
we obtain from you,
we will no longer have to
rely on the extreme rarity
of naturally occurring
Pandora compatibility.
The days of you carrying
this burden alone are over.
The time has come for all
girls to help carry the load!
[gasps and applause]
[ROXANNE] Something doesn't
feel right about this.
As far as I can tell,
Doctor Gengo Aoi
is still opposed to them pushing
this E-Pandora project forward.
Not to mention they were
basically already done with it
before they ever got
permission from Chevalier
to move forward
in the first place.
Seems to me somebody's
been havin' a field day
with human experiments.
[JINA] Anything else
you'd like to say?
[SATELLIZER gasps]
I guess I would like to
know who the heck you are.
E-Pandora.
Ah. So you're what they've
been cookin' up down here.
[AMELIA huffs]
[SATELLIZER]
Evolution Pandora?
[OHARA] All they have to do...
[AMELIA] We refuse to
stand by and allow you...
[JINA] We're not that
different, are we?
All of us here are
Pandora, right?
[SATELLIZER] Next time.
"Evolution Pandora"