It's using that attack!
Sorry it took me so long.
Yumi!
Third Platoon, once you've
eliminated Target Three,
coordinate with the units
engaged with Target One.
What's our current status?
Our forces have
exposed the cores
of Targets Three and Four...
All platoons are continuing on
their assigned
intercept attacks.
Where do things stand with
the Ravensborne Nucleochede?
Scans show enemy Pandora
are moving toward level eight.
Barriers fifty-nine
and sixty are closed...
The invading units
are being rerouted
to our primary defensive line...
Stationed at that
position we have:
Ingrid Bernstein,
Attia Simmons, Creo Brand,
and Arnett McMillan...
They're prepared to engage.
I have something
very important to say.
I'm sure you've heard
any number of rumors,
but the Ravensborne
Nucleochede contains
the body of the woman who
gave birth to all Pandora.
This is the place
where we've stored
her "holy remains"
in order to keep them safe.
At this time,
we don't know how the Nova
were able to locate
the holy remains
or why they're after them.
We're still researching her
genetic mysteries ourselves,
but handing her over to the Nova
would assure the
defeat of mankind...
Therefore, it's vital
that you protect them.
I'm counting on you all.
That confirms
everything you said.
I heard it at the
el Bridget Manor...
What?
Uh, nothing...
It's just that guarding
such an important artifact
is the perfect assignment for me
since I am the highest
ranked second-year.
So it seems including
the number-two student
and some backwater
hick is a bit superfluous.
Who are you calling
a backwater hick?!
But then, the
top ranked third-years
were assigned to
this location as well.
This is just another
"safety zone"...
We're no different then the
other second years on standby.
Those third-years
are protecting us
while we "stand guard" here
and that's all there is to it.
Okay, what's your problem now?
I was wondering what's
the problem with you...
I've never known you to be
so talkative before today.
I have to agree. It is
a bit unusual for you.
Is it possible
that this situation
has rattled that
legendary nerve of yours?
No... That's not it at all.
Now deploying
Volt Weapon! Divine Trust!
Morning Star!
Deploying Infinity Fang!
Scythe... Machina!
Direct confrontation isn't
my usual approach
for handling things.
That's so typical of you.
Our guests have arrived!
They're using acceleration...!
Morrison, now!
Leo!
All together, guys!
What's wrong?
Was that sudden stop
inconvenient for you?
We've detected a Freezing cast
at the primary defensive line...
Enemy Pandora have stopped.
Hold on... They can use the
same powers as the Nova, right?
So let's treat them like
Nova and tear them apart!
Attia...! Above you!
You won't get away from me!
You do not need to pursue.
Restraining your current targets
is to remain your top priority.
But... Sister Margaret, why?!
There are other Pandora
guarding the facility.
Understood.
Restraining them
is our top priority?
Man, I really hate it when
somebody tells me to hold back.
Lead them to the
secondary defensive line!
Understood...!
Barriers seventy and
seventy-one are closing now.
Enemy Pandora have
reached level ten...
They're about to cross the
secondary defensive line.
So I missed, did I?
Enemy Pandora are at the
secondary defensive line!
You now face...
second-ranked third year...
Executor of Ingenious
Schemes, Elizabeth Mably...
Prepare to die.
Andrei, watch
the enemy closely...
...and be prepared if
either casts a Freezing.
Yes, my lady.
Freezing!
Stigma Satellite
System, activate!
It appears that if we destroy
the Stigmata in their chest
we can safely release the
Pandora from the Nova's control.
Understood!
Attention: The invading
Pandora's weakness
is the Stigmata in their chest.
Did you hear that?
Oh yeah.
Well, that sure
makes things simple!
Let me at 'em!
We did it.
Freezing area!
One enemy Pandora has
reached the lowest level.
I know you...!
You're the Godspeed of the East!
You know her too?
Well, yeah.
And I heard about the
history between you two.
That's in the past...
but I never imagined
we would meet again.
Hold on, country girl!
I'll free you from that
monster before you know it!
I never expected
to hear that from you!
However, I am not as
helpless as you think!
Four Mindsets!
You did it!
She had it coming.
Was that... an Acceleration?
That's strange. She Accelerates
differently than we do.
I may not be able to Accelerate,
but that doesn't mean
I can't slow her down!
Chains of Binding!
Rana!
You've got to get
out of here, now!
I'd never run away from a fight!
If you do not know
how to Accelerate,
you will just be a burden
we cannot afford to deal with!
Thank you... Kazuya.
Okay, that was terrifying.
Miss Ganessa, are you okay?
Are you okay, Miss Satella?
Get away from me, Aoi...!
I can handle this all by myself!
But why?
I'm my own person, not some
substitute for your sister.
Now get back.
Cathy and I have some
unfinished business.
I've been waiting to
finish this for a long time.
I won't let her
get the best of me!
Her speed's incredible!
You're not going anywhere...
I haven't finished with you yet.
Satellizer!
Did she just do
a Tempest Turn...?
No... It's an Acceleration.
That was incredible!
I distinctly remember telling
you to stay out of this.
What's happening? Where am I?
She just spoke...
She isn't dead?
What is this place...?
What am I doing here?
So that's it, the large
Stigmata in her chest
is what's been
controlling her mind!
If I don't take her down in
this next attack, I'm done for!
Her fusion with the Stigmata
framework is increasing...
At this rate, she'll...
Non-interval Double
Acceleration!
There it is...!
It's like a Tempest Turn
with Acceleration!
Triple... Acceleration!
Quadruple Acceleration?!
I can't keep up with her speed!
You have to stop, Cathy!
Snap out of it!
You know you don't
want to do this!
Kazuya...
Don't let this thing make you
forget who you really are...!
Remember what you said you
wanted to do with your life!
Besides, if you're
half as good at writing
as you are at fighting Nova,
it'd be a crime if I didn't
get to read your work!
Thank you!
Kazuya...! Get away from here!
No chance in hell...!
I am not leaving you!
I've already said you're not
needed for this fight!
I don't care if you need me, I'm
staying right here because...
Because I need you, Satella!
Why...?
Why do you think?
It's because you're my partner!
Don't you understand, yet...?
You received
my sister's Stigmata.
You're incredibly
important to me...!
Because you showed
me that... with you...
It's not just Stigmata
that I carry on my back...
I carry all of your hopes
and dreams as well.
We Pandora carry the hopes
and dreams of the whole world.
With you I can protect the
world my sister fought to save!
I'm such a fool...
What was I thinking...?
Kazuya never wanted me
to replace his sister...
As if I could be an adequate
substitute for Kazuha Aoi,
the heroine that all
Pandora aspire to.
All Kazuya ever
wanted was a partner...
Someone to help him protect
the hopes we all have.
When we first met,
he may have chosen me
because I inherited
his sister's Sacreds.
But the truth is, I'm the
one who discovered him...
If I didn't have
those Sacreds...
I wouldn't have a partner...
I'd still be alone.
I'm happy that I met Kazuya.
For this, I am grateful
to you, Kazuha Aoi,
but I swear...
I will never be defeated...
One day, I will surpass
even your legend.
When this battle is finished,
you will get your
Baptism, Kazuya.
Kazuya!
I can't move...!
I'm dead for sure!
I thought the Freezing
was neutralized,
why isn't she moving?
No...! Stop forcing me
to kill these people...
I don't want to hurt
anyone ever again...
There's only one
thing I've ever wanted,
to be a novelist...
I never wanted this.
What's happening to her?
I need your help...!
I'm begging you, Satellizer,
do whatever it takes to stop me!
She's disappearing!
Elizabeth, what in the
hell happened to you?
I'm sorry, ladies...
I'm afraid I let you down.
One enemy Pandora detected.
She's reached the
Ravensborne Nucleochede
and the holy remains!
I never wanted
to make friends...
For the longest time,
the only person I cared about
at this academy was me.
Final episode:
"Satellizer vs. Pandora."