[AMELIA] Answer me,
Doctor Ohara.
What are these things?
[OHARA] You remember learning
about Maria Lancelot,
the predecessor of the Pandora.
I know you've heard of her.
[AMELIA]
What are you saying?
These things are Maria?
[OHARA] Technically,
they're mass-produced clones
of Maria Lancelot
that I created.
I call them Type-Maria Pandora.
Why would you do
something like this?
Once I have perfected
the Type Maria,
we won't need you girls anymore.
The Original Pandora
will no longer have to
sacrifice themselves either.
[AMELIA] If you had this
project in the works,
then why did Chevalier
need to create E-Pandora?
[OHARA laughs]
[OHARA] This project is
entirely of my own design.
None of these experiments had
the approval of Chevalier.
[AMELIA]
So these messed-up lab rats
were your real focus
the whole time?
What about us?!
Didn't we E-Pandora
mean anything to you?
[AMELIA cries]
That's terrible.
All those things you said.
I trusted you.
But everything you've ever
told me is probably just a lie.
Jina and Rattle wasted their
lives for your sick vision!
None of your efforts
were in vain.
Some sacrifices were necessary
for the sake of
humanity's future.
[AMELIA sobs]
[AMELIA] I'm sick of
hearing that crap!
There is no excuse
for what you've done!
[AMELIA yells]
[OHARA] That invisible
barrier will prevent
your Stigmata from
synchronizing.
[AMELIA groans]
I don't expect
you to understand
what I've gone through.
I'm completely aware of the
atrocities I've committed
and the burden that
will be mine to bear.
But even so, I must
accomplish my goal.
There is no turning back now.
[NOVA CALL]
[OHARA]
What's happening?
[AMELIA groans]
Aaaahhhh!
Aaahhh! Aaaaaaahhhhh!
But how?
Stigmata Synchronization?
That's impossible!
[crashing sound]
I'm afraid that your
bizarre fondness
of Amelia is rather unhealthy.
And it may accidentally
bring about...
...the worst possible scenario.
[OHARA gasps]
[AMELIA screams]
[FEMALE OPERATOR 10A] Power
failure in Lab Zero, Section D!
[FEMALE OPERATOR 10C] We've lost
all telemetry from the bio-lab!
[alarm sounds]
Nova detected
within the base!
[NOVA CALL]
[FEMALE OPERATOR 10B]
Dimensional vibrations detected!
They're of a micro-order scale!
Routing emergency power
to laboratory section!
[OPERATOR 10A] Dimensional
vibrations continuing!
[FEMALE OPERATOR 10B] The Nova
signal is now changing
from QR to QB!
[NOVA CALL]
This doesn't make sense!
I created you for the sole
purpose of surpassing Gengo Aoi.
There's no way that you could
possess self-awareness.
[NOVA CALL]
He warned me about this.
He told me it was like
the Tower of Babel!
[alarm sounds]
[GENGO] In response
to the Tower of Babel,
God dispensed
divine punishment.
Chaos.
You're kidding me.
The Nova are divine punishment?
Impossible.
He was right.
[FEMALE OPERATOR 10A]
Signal pattern matched!
Nova has been confirmed!
Type is unknown!
[NOVA CALL]
[FEMALE OPERATOR 10C] There's no
doubt, it's definitely a Nova!
[SPENCER]
This can't be happening!
[FEMALE OPERATOR 10B]
Switching to main screen!
[FEMALE OPERATORS gasp]
But how can a Nova's
type be unknown?
Issue Code N1
immediately!
[FEMALE OPERATOR 10A]
Code N1 now in effect!
Switching to special
state of alert!
Attention all Pandora:
Code N1 is now in effect!
I repeat, Code N1
is now in effect!
Switching to special
state of alert!
A Nova? But how?
[NOVA CALL]
[FEMALE OPERATOR 10A] Nova
Type-Unknown is on the move!
[FEMALE OPERATOR 10B]
It's heading towards
the Photon Generator!
Nova is closing in fast!
[alarm sounds]
[NOVA CALL]
We can't let that monster
reach the generator, or else--
[GENGO] Or else we'll be
facing a global disaster
thanks to your recklessness.
[SPENCER] Gengo Aoi?
What are you doing here?
Simple. I'm the head of
Chevalier's inspection team.
We're investigating this
facility at the request
of the El Bridget family.
Huh?! The El Bridget family?
[GENGO] Not only
have you performed
outlandish human
experiments here.
But you have also gone so
far as to create a Nova.
I haven't the slightest clue
what you're talking about!
I didn't create that thing!
Then how did
it come to be?
That Nova didn't appear
from another dimension.
It originated in this world!
[NOVA CALL]
No wonder its
dimensional vibrations
had such a strange pattern.
[GENGO] I highly
doubt Doctor Ohara
ever expected her actions
to lead to this calamity.
You mean this is
Scarlet Ohara's doing?
As of this moment,
I am taking command.
This is Gengo Aoi.
Mobilize all Pandora
and Limiters now!
[FEMALE ANNOUNCEMENT]
All Pandora and Limiters,
mobilize immediately!
I repeat, all Pandora and
Limiters, mobilize immediately!
Good luck, Soo-na.
Thank you, doctor, but you
don't have to worry about me.
[NOVA CALL]
[AMELIA screams]
[PANDORA gasp and whimper]
So this is its strategy.
Mental deterioration
via Stigmata!
[AMELIA screams]
[NOVA CALL]
This power. What is it?
My Stigmata!
[CATHY and JULIA yell]
Honestly, you are quite the
burdensome underclassmen.
[SATELLIZER whimpers]
[SATELLIZER screams]
Your high-level
Stigmata compatibility's
working against you.
So you're taking the full force
of the Nova's mental
deterioration!
[CHIFFON groans]
No, President Chiffon!
What was that?
The president's
Illusion Turn.
This does not bode well.
She's losing it.
[alarm sounds]
[CATHY] We need to
reach the others.
They could probably use
our help fighting the Nova!
Are you just
always like this?
[FEMALE ANNOUNCEMENT]
Attention, all Pandora!
A Type-Unknown Nova is heading
toward the Photon Generator!
Stop it at all costs!
So that's it.
[ROXANNE]
Crazy, huh?
Looks like there is
such a thing as being
too Stigmata-compatible.
[CATHY]
Roxanne, you're not hurt?
Come on girl,
only a total newbie
would let a little screaming
mess with their head.
[JULIA]
Good going, Zombie.
[FEMALE OPERATOR 10A] Twenty
percent of our Pandora team
are now unable to fight!
[FEMALE OPERATOR 10B]
An unknown psycho-interference
has penetrated via Stigmata!
[OPERATOR 10C] Stigma system
intrusion rate skyrocketing!
[GENGO] Forced Stigma
activation mode!
Transmit the autogenic barrier
command, immediately!
[SATELLIZER]
Aahhh!
[CHIFFON]
[KAZUYA] Satella, please!
That's enough!
You have to stop!
Kazuya, listen to me!
Deploy an omnidirectional
Freezing field,
then make direct contact
with Satellizer's mind!
Do it now!
If you don't hurry The
Student Council president
is going to kill Satellizer!
She'll kill her?
Chiffon Fairchild isn't
your ordinary Pandora!
If she turns into a Nova,
Satellizer and the rest
of us will be doomed!
If you want to
save Satellizer,
then do as I say!
[KAZUYA]
Freezing! Aaahhhh!
The greater your
Freezing ability,
the more likely this'll work!
Focus your thoughts into
reaching Satellizer's mind
and saving it from
deterioration!
[KAZUYA groans]
It's not worth it!
If the Freezing
consciousness link fails,
then it's the Limiter who
will have to pay the price!
That means Kazuya Aoi
will be lost forever!
Don't worry, I'll be fine!
[KAZUYA] So this is
Satella's consciousness.
I have no idea where
to look for her mind.
But I have to try.
I can't stand the thought of
the Student Council
president killing her.
[KAZUYA] I will find it,
even if it kills me!
Um, Satella?
[SATELLIZER gasps]
[NOEL]
I'm so sorry, Satella.
I just can't be there.
From now on, you must be strong.
Stronger than anyone else
you come across in life.
Always hold your
head up high, for me.
And never give up.
Don't lose to anyone,
no matter what.
Be strong, Satella.
Be strong.
[tone]
Don't go, mom!
Please don't go!
[SATELLIZER]
From then on...
I was always alone.
[SATELLIZER] Sometimes I wish
I was never given the Sacreds.
Then life would be easy.
I feel like I don't
belong anywhere.
Like there's nowhere
for me to go.
I'm sick of it.
I want to be where
somebody cares about me.
[NOEL] Satella?
Satella. It's okay.
It's okay now.
Is that you, mother?
I want to go where you are.
Then I won't be alone anymore!
Satellizer, don't go!
Kazuya? Kazuya!
I'm so sorry!
I'm sorry that I never mastered
your sister's Sacreds.
And for never going
through with a baptism!
Please forgive me!
I don't care
about any of that!
Just come back to me!
[RANA] Why all the nonsense
about being lonely?
You are already terribly greedy,
always hogging my Kazuya
just for yourself! Heh.
[KAZUYA chuckles lightly]
Thank you for
doing that, Rana.
There's no way I
could've saved her
if you hadn't jumped in to help.
You are too humble.
I barely did anything.
It was your strong
feelings for Satellizer
that deserve the real credit!
Thanks, both of you.
We've no time to waste.
[YI] The threat is
directly in front of us!
We may die here, so we might
as well give it our all!
Ready to follow
my lead, Pandora?
[GROUP] Yes!
[FEMALE OPERATOR 10A]
Pandora platoon has established
a defense line along
the Nova's path!
[FEMALE OPERATOR 10B]
Pandora survival rate
currently at fifty-five percent!
Anomalies detected
around the Nova!
[FEMALE OPERATOR 10C]
Switching to main screen!
[NOVA CALL]
Maria. Maria Lancelot!
[GENGO]
How surreal.
The Pandora were
created by mass-producing
Maria Lancelot's Stigmata
and implanting them.
Now they must face an enemy
that looks exactly like her.
This could only be your
twisted idea, Scarlet Ohara.
[alarm sounds]
[FEMALE OPERATOR 10C] Stigma
system intrusion underway!
[FEMALE OPERATOR 10A]
Deploying defensive barrier!
[FEMALE OPERATOR 10B] Activating
Cross-Interleaved mode!
It's trying to enter my mind
more forcefully this time.
Yeah.
Hold steady, girls!
We can't afford to let that
thing get in our heads!
How are you
holding up, Holly?
I'm okay!
[NOVA CALL]
[FEMALE OPERATOR 10A]
Nova derivatives multiplying!
[YI yells]
There's no end to them!
[FEMALE PANDORA 11A yells]
[FEMALE PANDORA 11C screams]
[PANDORA scream]
[FEMALE OPERATOR 10C]
Pandora casualties rising!
They're at a major disadvantage!
[FEMALE OPERATOR 10B]
Type-Unknown is rapidly
approaching the
Photon Generator!
[FEMALE OPERATOR 10C]
Friendly units detected
along Type-Unknown's course!
Switching friendlies
to main screen!
[GENGO] Kazuya!
How are we supposed
to defeat it?
[CHIFFON] Anti-Nova.
It's our only option.
We have to put our lives
on the line, for humanity.
[CHIFFON] Do you think we can
call things even between us...
[ELIZABETH] Chiffon.
Forgive me for what I said.
[TICY] We will meet again
my friend, I know it.
[SATELLIZER]
Next time. "Shaft of Light."