[murmuring]
[KAZUYA]
Here ya' go!
One large Burger Queen
meal as requested!
Eh?
Is everything all right?
Yeah. It's nothing.
[KAZUYA] It's just,
well, don't you think
you should tell me how
you got those injuries?
[KAZUYA sighs]
Gotta admit it's kind of weird.
Since the E-Pandora lab
doesn't specialize
in those types of wounds.
You have to go all the way
back to West Genetics
to get them treated.
[SATELLIZER] Maybe that was part
of Elizabeth's plan all along.
[ELIZABETH] Why don't you just
go outside and cool down?
[SATELLIZER]
That's ridiculous.
[KAZUYA] Guess we should
look on the bright side.
At least you and I'll get
some alone time together.
[SATELLIZER] Huh?
We've been cooped up with
everybody at the E-Pandora lab.
Now it's just you and me.
You and me... alone.
[gasps]
Is something wrong,
Satella?
No, I'm fine!
It's um, it's...
It's nothing, really.
[FEMALE AIRPORT ANNOUNCER]
Attention: all passengers
transferring from Anchorage
Flight three-three-five-one
to Japan Flight
six-one-seven-four,
your boarding gate has changed.
It will now be
departing from Gate A8
and will be boarding shortly.
[KAZUYA] Whoa, that gate's
in the other terminal.
We've gotta go.
[FEMALE AIRPORT ANNOUNCER]
Attention: all passengers
bound for Bali via
Minneapolis and Amsterdam,
Artlim Airline Flight
three-four-three-one
is now boarding at Gate B12.
I repeat, Artlim Flight
three-four-three-one
is now boarding.
Stop, Kazuya.
Why?
[SATELLIZER]
Take me there.
What? That's not the
gate for our flight.
That one's going to Bali!
Hm? Hmm?
Hey! No, Satella,
wait, hold up!
What are you doing?
That's against the rules!
We can't go there;
we're supposed to be flying
back to West Genetics!
[typing]
[ANDREI] You're seriously
going to leak the information
you uncovered to
your family, my lady?
[ELIZABETH] "Leak?"
Please, do you have to
put it like that, Andrei?
Well, how else would
you describe it?
That's exactly what Chevalier
is going to call it,
and they'll consider everything
that you're planning
as an act of treason too.
Yes, I know, and I'm
aware of that risk.
I'm sure we'll get public
support on our side,
so don't worry
about it, 'kay?
I'm worried about you
this is dangerous.
My lady. Please be honest.
Do you really think the media
and the public can be persuaded?
Not by me. However,
my family can do it.
[ANDREI scoffs]
[ELIZABETH] To be more specific,
my father can do it.
With the power and
respect he commands,
the world will listen to
whatever he has to say.
Eli, by doing this
you will be putting
the entire Mably family at risk.
I realize that.
[ANDREI scoffs]
[ELIZABETH] Ever since
I was a little girl,
my father instilled in me
a sense of what's called
"noblesse oblige."
[YOUNG ELIZABETH] So this thing
you're trying to teach me
is called "noblesse oblige"?
[CHRISTOPHER] That's right.
You know what
that means, Eli?
It means the people
who are powerful
must always protect
those who are not.
It's our duty to help others.
[YOUNG ELIZABETH] Hm...
You're little.
This might be too much for
you to understand just yet.
No, I do understand what
it means, Daddy, I do.
I promise I'll never
forget it, either.
My "Noblesse Oblige."
[CHRISTOPHER chuckles]
[ELIZABETH] That's exactly
why I'm going to do this.
It's my duty, Andrei.
[ELIZABETH] I promised my
father I would always protect
those who are weaker, and in
this case, it's the E-Pandora.
No one else is
looking out for them,
and without my help,
they'll continue to die.
If any harm comes to me or
my family because we tried to
save the lives of those who need
to be protected, then so be it!
Do you understand?
My Noblesse Oblige demands
that I help the E-Pandora.
And I'll die trying, if need be.
[ELIZABETH] That said, I don't
want to put you in any danger.
Alright? That's why I'm ordering
you to stay out of this.
[ANDREI] Heh. I guess you're
gonna have to cripple me then.
I'm your Limiter and won't
let you do this alone.
I'll be there by your side.
Heh. So are you gonna let me
come along. Or hurt me?
Well, my lady?
Heh. Alright,
then you can help me.
[beeping]
So I guess you're
finally finished?
[ELIZABETH] No.
This is only the
beginning, Andrei.
[ANDREI chuckles]
[CHIFFON]
Hey, Elizabeth.
I haven't seen you
around much lately,
where've you been?
I've been busy with a
project the last few days.
That sounds interesting.
Can you tell me about it?
[chiming over intercom]
[FEMALE ANNOUNCEMENT]
West Genetics Pandora.
Elizabeth Mably. Please report
to General HQ at once.
I repeat. West Genetics
Pandora. Elizabeth Mably.
Please report to
General HQ at once.
[ELIZABETH]
Elizabeth Mably reporting.
[SPENCER]
You may enter.
[ELIZABETH gasps]
[ELIZABETH]
Active service Chevalier.
There shouldn't be
any stationed here.
[SPENCER] I would
like to thank you for
taking the time to
come in today, Miss Mably.
So, tell me.
How is life in Alaska
treating you?
I imagine it's not quite as
comfortable as it is in Japan.
[ELIZABETH]
No, it's fine.
I really can't complain, sir.
After all, coping with
the harshest of conditions
is just one part of
a Pandora's duty.
[SPENCER]
I'm impressed.
You know who would say that
kind of thing, Miss Mably?
A Pandora who is
faithful to Chevalier.
Something you're not.
[ELIZABETH gasps]
[SPENCER] And how do
I know you're not loyal?
Because if you were,
you would never have committed
such an egregious offense.
[ELIZABETH gasps]
[ELIZABETH] What?
Mind explaining
yourself, Miss Mably?
This is proprietary information,
yet your family got ahold of it!
[ELIZABETH]
This is impossible!
How on earth did he find out?
Surely Father took every
precaution to keep this secret.
[SPENCER] Heh. I'm sure
you're wondering
how this came to my attention.
It seems the head of the Mably
family sought someone's advice
as to its accuracy.
It's just too bad they didn't
know that said someone
also works for Chevalier.
Isn't it?
[ELIZABETH gasps]
[SPENCER]
Please, enlighten me.
Why did you leak
classified information?
[ELIZABETH] Because.
What you're doing here is wrong.
The Mark IV
isn't ready, sir.
You knew it could result
in Nova transformation
but you still went through
with it and as a result Jina--
[SPENCER] Need I remind
you that it is Chevalier
who makes all
the decisions here?!
As a Pandora, it is your job
to do as you are told!
Leaking highly-classified
military intelligence
is a serious offense,
Miss Mably.
You've committed treason and
will be dealt with accordingly.
[SPENCER] You're in enough
trouble as it is.
Take my advice.
Don't try to resist.
[ELIZABETH] Heh.
[murmuring]
[CHIFFON]
Well, this is a rare sight.
Are you by yourself?
[ANDREI] Huh?
So I guess this means
Elizabeth is still gone?
[ANDREI]
Yeah. It's weird,
she hasn't come back since
reporting to General HQ.
Oh, I wonder why
they called her there.
Hey, I know.
[ANDREI] Huh?
Maybe they're giving her a treat
for her excellent grades!
[YUJIN sighs]
I wish you'd follow her example
and get better grades yourself.
[CHIFFON] What?
[YUJIN] And a treat?
Really? She's not a kid.
[CHIFFON]
Don't be silly!
Everybody loves getting a treat
no matter how old they are!
Turn it on.
Uh. Yes, sir.
[ELIZABETH groans]
[MALE STAFF 5B]
Shall I stop, sir?
[SPENCER] Continue.
But Secretary Spencer
if we keep this up,
it could cause irreparable
harm to the subject.
[SPENCER]
I don't care.
The girl can handle it;
she's a Pandora.
Her kind doesn't
break so easily.
[MALE STAFF quaver]
[SPENCER] She needs
to be put in her place
and reminded of who's calling
the shots around here.
The duty of a Pandora is simply
to follow Chevalier's orders.
This one foolishly believed that
she could ignore those orders.
She must be taught that
her only two options are
obedience or death.
Absence might make
the heart grow fonder,
but mine is aching.
Dear Kazuya is the
man of my dreams.
If he does not return soon, I am
sure I will die of heartbreak!
[ANDREI] I told you already!
She was summoned three days
ago and hasn't returned!
I demand to know
what's happened
to Elizabeth Mably
and I wanna know now!
HQ has business with her.
She'll return shortly.
What kind of "business" could
HQ have with my Pandora?
[FEMALE CHEVALIER 5B] We can't
tell you since it's classified.
Guess I'm gonna have to
get answers my own way!
Stop or they're
gonna' kill you!
Dammit, Yujin.
Let's all go back
to our quarters.
Rumor has it the top brass
are upset about something.
[ANDREI sighs]
Wait a minute.
Don't tell me
Elizabeth's involved.
What exactly have
you heard about it?
Has Eli's name
been mentioned?
Y'know, it's not very
polite to do that.
Eavesdropping on people is rude.
I apologize, but curiosity
got the better of me.
[gasps]
[RANA] Huh?
[RANA gasps]
[FEMALE CHEVALIER 5B]
Move it!
Elizabeth Mably,
you are suspended.
You're also remanded to
your quarters for one week.
Uh. Hey.
Eli. Oh, my lady!
Look. It's Andrei!
Come on!
Eli!
What did those
monsters do to you?
Whatever it was, I know
you can snap out of it
because you're the
strongest person I know!
Please!
I hate to see her
in this condition.
[ANDREI sobs]
[ANDREI]
Come back to me!
I'm begging you, my lady!
Elizabeth! Please!
[perplexed murmuring]
[FEMALE NEWSCASTER]
For those just joining us,
scandal continues to rock...
Hey, what's the
heck's going on?
You've heard of the
Mably Group, right?
Well, it looks like
they might be done for.
Whoa, seriously?
[FEMALE NEWSCASTER]
Evidence continues to mount
that massive accounting
fraud has taken place
across the conglomerate.
Even more damning are
allegations that this fraud
was carried out by
several top executives,
leading to public outcry
that's grown exponentially with
the latest startling accusation
to hit the company overnight.
Several Mably
factory employees allege
they were forced to work
under sweatshop conditions...
Wow, so I guess it's
true what they say
about rich people
always being corrupt.
[AMELIA]
Not in this case.
[RATTLE]
Uh. Amelia?
[FEMALE NEWSCASTER]
Some business insiders
are already saying that Mably's
once-sterling public image
has been irrevocably tarnished,
and there is no way the company
can ever recover from this--
[ANDREI]
This is retaliation.
Retaliation?
[ANDREI] Elizabeth's family
attempted to reveal the truth
about the E-Pandora.
[RANA] What?
[ANDREI]
It's revenge.
Chevalier's trying to
destroy the Mablys.
[RANA gasps]
[YUJIN gasps]
[ANDREI] Chevalier conducted
the Mark IV test
despite already knowing that
it probably wouldn't work.
In fact, Jina died
because of it,
and Eli refused to allow that
to happen to anyone else.
To save the E-Pandora,
she shared what she learned
with the Mably family,
and asked that they reveal it.
Eli was fully aware of the risk
she and her family were taking,
but she felt like
it was her duty.
[AMELIA] No way.
Elizabeth Mably did that?
[RANA]
Do my ears fool me?
Did you say they knew
the Mark IV would not work?
The Mark IV wasn't even
close to being ready
so Chevalier did the
only thing it could do.
They lied and said it
was fully operational
in order to keep funds flowing
into the E-Pandora Project.
The E-Pandora were
nothing more than
expendable guinea pigs to them!
They didn't care
how many were killed!
The bastards! They didn't
count on Eli finding out!
Calm down, Andrei.
It isn't as if there's any
definitive proof, right?
However, spying on Chevalier
is a serious offense,
and if she leaked
classified intelligence--
She knew what she was doing
went against regulations,
but it was the only way
to get the truth out
and put an end to
the E-Pandora Project!
She said she wouldn't let
any more E-Pandora die!
I respect you.
And I can honestly say you're
one of the few people here
I feel that way about.
[AMELIA] Elizabeth.
You risked everything for us.
[SATELLIZER grunts]
Oh, this is such
a heavenly breeze!
So you and I are actually in
Bali right now, aren't we?
[SATELLIZER]
It's nothing.
[KAZUYA] Maybe not to you,
but it is to me.
[SATELLIZER laughs]
Huh?
Uhh...
[SATELLIZER] Kazuya! I see
a Burger Queen over there!
Do you think you could
go get me something?
I'm so hungry!
[KAZUYA] What?
[SATELLIZER]
Oh, pretty please?
[KAZUYA] Uh, sure!
[paper rustles]
[SATELLIZER gasps]
Burger Queen meal
as requested!
So, what's goin'
on in the world.
[gasps]
The Mablys are involved
in a scandal?
I wonder how Elizabeth's
dealing with it.
I don't like
repeating myself.
This isn't your concern,
so stay out of it.
[MALE DRIVER 5A]
Excuse me.
Miss Satellizer el Bridget,
I presume?
Miss Violet el Bridget has
sent me to pick you up, ma'am.
I am but your humble servant.
Servants and limousines.
At your beck and call.
Wow!
[KAZUYA exclaims]
Everything all right?
[KAZUYA] It just hit
me how wealthy you--
I mean--your family is.
They're major players in
the world, aren't they?
Yes, and I hope to put
their status and power
to good use and accomplish
what Elizabeth could not.
Wait a sec, does Elizabeth
have something to do with that
huge Mably scandal you were
reading about in the paper?
[SATELLIZER]
I don't know. But...
[KAZUYA] So... is that
why we came here?
[SATELLIZER] Mm-hm.
Well, that answers
one question.
Can you maybe tell me about
the rest of your plan?
[VIOLET] Satella!
[VIOLET] What happened?
Are you alright?
Oh, come on,
I'm a Pandora.
You know better than
to worry about me.
That is sweet of you,
though, Sis.
This is the older sister
you told me about?
Uh-huh. This place
is also her resort.
[KAZUYA] Huh?
Only in a manner
of speaking.
Our father left me in charge so
I serve as the acting manager.
Enough about me I'm
so happy you're here!
It's been too long, Satella!
[SATELLIZER chuckles]
This must be him.
[SATELLIZER] Yes. He's the
one I mentioned in my email.
This is--
You're Kazuya Aoi, right?
My sister's first boyfriend.
[KAZUYA] Heh. Her what?
Violet!
[VIOLET] When Satella told me
she was bringing a boy here,
I got so excited!
I was so curious what the
young man who caught her eye
might look like!
But you!
I never expected such a cutie!
I could just eat you up!
If you want, you can call
me "Sis," too, okay?
[SATELLIZER]
Violet, stop!
[SATELLIZER] What?
Mother and Father
will be arriving soon?
[VIOLET] They're coming for a
vacation, and to see how well
their daughter has
been running things.
I figured you knew
and came to see them.
That is the reason you're
here, isn't it, Satella?
[SATELLIZER] Actually,
I came to see you, Violet.
I was hoping that I could
convince you to talk
to Mother and Father
about something for me.
[VIOLET]
That's silly! We're family!
Why not just talk
to them yourself?
I couldn't.
[KAZUYA] Hm?
[LUIS] I see. So you have
business with Mom and Dad.
[SATELLIZER gasps]
[KAZUYA] Huh?
It's good to see you. Sister.
[SATELLIZER gasps]
Luis. Oh, no...
Hey, Satellizer.
Are you okay?
[LUIS chuckles]
[SATELLIZER] It's true,
my family may be great.
[LUIS] We'll simply
return to the way...
[KAZUYA] I'd gladly lay
down my life for her.
I'd protect her no
matter what the cost.
[SATELLIZER]
Next time: "Marionettes."