[horn honks]
[chiming from intercom]
[FEMALE STUDENT 12A]
Look who it is!
Really awesome work today,
Vice President Ticy.
[TICY] Oh, thanks.
Where are you two headed?
[FEMALE STUDENTS laugh]
[FEMALE STUDENT 12B]
Oh, you know!
There's nothing wrong with a
girls' night out on the town,
but whatever you do, don't
forget about your curfew.
Remember, the end of the year
meeting is coming up!
[TICY] That's right.
Their assignment in Alaska
should be over soon too.
I can't wait to see you
again, President Chiffon.
So this is
Anti-Nova.
Wait, you've heard of it?
I know it well.
It's the very first Volt Weapon
Maria Lancelot produced.
[RANA] Maria?
[KAZUYA] The 'holy remains'
we defended before.
What is Chiffon doing?
Oh no.
An Illusion Turn!
[RANA gasps]
[NOVA CALL]
These energy levels are
off the charts, sir!
[gasps]
[CHIFFON gasps]
[CHIFFON] The Nova is
reconfiguring its outer shell
to protect its inner core.
It's evolving.
How can this be?
[CHIFFON] I guess the
only way to stop you now...
...is to meet you on your level,
and make the ultimate sacrifice.
[SATELLIZER]
Look at her form.
It's amazing.
[YI] I've never seen
anything like it.
I didn't even know a
Pandora could do that!
Aaahh!
Captain, look out!
What's wrong?
Zombies...
[ROXANNE] Hey, that's my name,
don't wear it out!
What the heck
is going on?
What, not even
a come-back?
[sighs]
They've merged
into a single being.
Look at its size.
How are we supposed
to fight that thing?
[FEMALE OPERATORS
chatter indistinctly]
[FEMALE OPERATOR 10A] Type-Maria
amalgamation has vanished!
[GENGO] What?
[FEMALE OPERATOR 10B]
No EPM signal at all!
[FEMALE OPERATOR 10C]
Unknown Nova remains unfazed!
[FEMALE OPERATOR 10D] It appears
we've lost all traces
of the Type-Maria
amalgamation, sir!
[GENGO] No.
[gasps] Wait!
Type-Maria just reappeared!
Location. It's right
next to Type-Unknown!
[NOVA CALL]
It's her. Maria Lancelot.
The Nova... What are they?
[CHIFFON gasps]
[NOVA CALL]
[FEMALE OPERATOR 10A] Energy
levels are spiking again, sir!
[FEMALE OPERATOR 10B]
The Photon Generator
is within firing range!
It's going to land a direct hit!
No!
[FEMALE OPERATOR 10C]
Beam has dissipated!
How in the world did
she stop that thing?
[FEMALE OPERATOR 10D] And
without so much as a scratch!
[GENGO]
Without a scratch? I doubt that.
[AMELIA]
Why? Why do you protect them?
I know that you are fully aware
of the sins they've committed.
Have you forgotten our sorrow?
No, Amelia, I remember.
[CHIFFON] I remember
everything that happened.
I remember what the
humans did to you.
[AMELIA] Then please.
Tell me why?
You're not one
of them, Chiffon.
You're not a human.
So why would you
take their side?
Even though
they're different,
they deserve forgiveness.
I understand that the
humans caused you pain.
But is it too much
to ask that you find
a way to forgive
them for their sins?
Type Unknown has
stopped moving completely!
I know you remember
how weak humans are.
You were one yourself.
You know how flawed the
human race can truly be.
[CHIFFON] Yet, as you are
no longer a human being...
What sense is there
in you punishing them?
What is the point?
[CHIFFON]
Don't you see?
You're on the verge
of committing
the same mistake the
humans made with you.
But you're not alone.
You have friends.
[inaudible]
You're a good
friend, Amelia.
So do the right thing.
My friends.
[CHIFFON] Let's put
an end to this.
[AMELIA sobs]
I'm really sorry.
But, there's nothing I can do
to change the way I feel!
I don't want to drag
my friends into it.
And I want to end this,
just like you do.
I promise!
But! My hatred's
too strong! Aaahh!
[AMELIA screams]
[NOVA CALL]
[FEMALE OPERATOR 10A] Abnormal
Change in Type Unknown!
[FEMALE OPERATOR 10B]
Localized Planck Fluctuations!
[FEMALE OPERATOR 10C]
Level five!
[FEMALE OPERATOR 10D]
D-turbulence detected!
[FEMALE OPERATOR 10A]
Extra-dimensional exposure!
[FEMALE OPERATOR 10B]
It's a Calabi-Yau incident!
[FEMALE OPERATOR 10C]
The Nova is changing shape!
Turbulence level increasing!
[FEMALE OPERATOR 10D]
Level three, five, seven!
[FEMALE OPERATOR 10A]
Dimensional vibrations detected!
Type S Waveform!
I'm picking up a lot of
dimensional compression
near Type Unknown.
It looks like Unknown is
preparing to self-destruct, sir!
Attention all personnel,
this is Gengo Aoi.
Chevalier General Command's
Nova consultant!
Cease all combat immediately.
Proceed to the
underground shelter!
That is an order.
The Nova intends
to self-destruct
and take out the
Photon Generator!
Drop whatever
you may be doing
and get yourselves
underground, do it now!
[FEMALE ANNOUNCEMENT]
All personnel,
proceed to the shelter at once!
I repeat. All personnel
Come on! This way!
It's too late to stop it!
Well, I guess this is
the end of the line, huh?
[KAZUYA] No, you can't.
We need to go.
[SATELLIZER gasps]
No, Satellizer, don't!
[SATELLIZER]
President Chiffon!
You have to come with us!
You know what?
It's nice to have friends.
And that's why I'm
going to keep you safe
no matter what the cost.
Don't you understand?
If you don't come with us
right now, you'll die!
[SATELLIZER gasps]
[CHIFFON] Amelia's hatred
for humankind runs so deep
that it's beyond her ability
to keep it under control.
As far as their morality.
She views humanity
as being evil.
And maybe on some level,
humans should pay for
the things they've done!
But even so...
We're friends and I don't
want any of you to get hurt.
I don't want to lose you either.
I suppose that's selfish
in a way, isn't it?
[SATELLIZER gasps]
[CHIFFON] All I can think
about is what matters to me.
And that makes me no better than
the humans I would condemn.
You're wrong.
[CHIFFON] So, like a human,
I've made one last choice.
One selfish decision
that's for me alone.
I'm going to protect my friends.
What are you saying?
You're not making any sense!
It doesn't have to be this way!
Nobody has to die!
Do you hear me?
[CHIFFON]
Satellizer El Bridget.
I hope you have
a great life.
Enjoy the time I'm
about to give you.
[SATELLIZER gasps]
[ROXANNE] She's going
to absorb the explosion!
Thank you, Chiffon.
[CHIFFON] No.
I should be thanking you.
If you hadn't fought
so hard to avoid
being swallowed by your hatred,
this disaster would
have been unpreventable.
So now it's my turn.
[AMELIA gasps]
You see, Amelia,
I've decided I have to keep my
friends safe, no matter what.
And I know the price I will pay
for something like this
is going be extreme.
[AMELIA]
No, Chiffon, you can't.
Don't do this.
There's no other alternative.
I only have one hope.
That somehow through
my sacrifice,
humanity will learn to
right the terrible wrongs
they committed against you.
Rattle's okay!
Do you think we can
call things even
between us now, Amelia?
[AMELIA gasps]
[CHIFFON] Ticy!
[TICY gasps]
[TICY]
Who's there?
[CHIFFON] Ticy.
[TICY] Huh?
I can count on you.
You will be my
replacement, won't you?
[CHIFFON] After all.
With me gone, you are
the most powerful Pandora.
[TICY] No.
This is too much
for me to handle.
I can't do it.
Chiffon! I'm nothing
without you!
[CHIFFON]
Actually, Ticy,
I think you're going be
better than I ever was.
Remember what I always
used to tell you.
No matter how terrible things
might get, as long as you smile.
Happiness will
always be yours,
and no one can take that away!
[TICY cries]
[CHIFFON] So...
until we meet again...
Keep on smiling.
[TICY] Chiffon.
We will meet again,
my friend. I know it.
So strange.
What is this feeling?
[CHARLES] This is nothing like
the Nova's mental deterioration.
I don't know, but I'm pretty
sure my wounds are healing.
Yeah.
What is this
new sensation?
I don't think I've ever felt
anything like it before.
[ROXANNE chuckles]
How come I feel
all mushy?
[SATELLIZER]
I think I know.
[SATELLIZER] There's only
one thing it could be.
This is love.
A love that Chiffon left
behind for us to enjoy.
You're right. Love.
[ELIZABETH] Chiffon.
Forgive me for what I said.
I could never feel
contempt for you.
[KAZUYA]
And that was that.
From the little I heard after,
it seemed things turned
out pretty well.
Luckily, the E-Pandora
Rattle managed to survive.
And I'm glad to say
Amelia did too.
The negative effects of
the biochemical experiments
conducted on her have been
completely wiped away,
which is really incredible news.
And all the tissue
she lost from her body
should be restored any day now.
Doctor Ohara was
rescued as well.
But she's yet to
regain consciousness.
Spencer, the director
of the project,
was taken into custody.
And the E-Pandora Project
was permanently discontinued.
And Elizabeth?
[SATELLIZER]
You're taking a break?
I am.
[SATELLIZER]
But I don't understand,
who's going to lead West
Genetics while you're away?
We have to have a leader!
I expect to
be criticized.
But to be completely
honest with you...
...there's no way I can
leave Andrei behind.
And I couldn't
begin to think of
teaming up with another Limiter.
[KAZUYA] As for me.
After everything was in order,
I decided to go back to Japan.
I had some people to see.
Oh, Kazuya, you've
finally come home!
I am so happy to see you!
Rana.
Don't touch him,
you ignorant country girl!
If I am an ignorant
country girl,
then I am sorry to say it,
but you are nothing more
than a helper! So eat that.
Will you stop with
this helper nonsense?
It's a ridiculous
thing to say, Rana!
[ELIZABETH] If I truly
believed there was no one
fit to lead West Genetics,
I wouldn't be leaving like this.
But I'm sure there's
no need to worry.
So I can afford to
be a little selfish.
I'm leaving you
all in good hands.
Oh, come on,
besides you,
who could possibly
replace Chiffon?
[SATELLIZER gasps]
[SATELLIZER]
Ticy Phenyl.