[alarm sounds]
[FEMALE ANNOUNCEMENT] Attention.
This is not a drill.
[FEMALE VOICE 10B] Continue
pursuit and subdue the traitors.
[FEMALE VOICE 10C] Which block?
Can you confirm?
[FEMALE VOICE 10D]
Report back immediately...
[FEMALE VOICE 10E]
Emergency protocols initiated.
[SPENCER]
Status report.
[FEMALE OPERATOR 10A] Fighting
is underway in three locations.
[FEMALE OPERATOR 10B]
R-B Block, Lab Seven.
Three Chevalier
members are currently
locked in combat against
E-Pandora Rattle.
She should be subdued soon.
[FEMALE OPERATOR 10C]
R-B Block, Area Two.
Julia Munberk of Genetics
Germany Panzer is currently
locked in combat with
the traitor Cathy Lockharte
of East Genetics.
[SPENCER] Trap her. Seal all
bulkheads leading to that block.
[FEMALE OPERATOR 10C]
Now sealing all bulkheads
leading to R-B
Block Area Two, sir.
So, I guess the plan
is to box me in
and keep me fighting
until I get worn down,
too bad for them because
I could do this all day.
How about you?
[JULIA moans]
[FEMALE OPERATOR 10C] We've lost
the audio and video feeds.
It must be due to all the
fighting in that block.
Keep the Pandora we
sent to subdue Lockharte
on standby as a precaution.
On it, sir.
Is there anything
else to report?
[FEMALE OPERATOR 10D]
I-T Block, Area Five.
Charles Bonaparte
of Genetics France.
She's currently locked
in combat against
the traitor Elizabeth Mably
of West Genetics.
[SPENCER] On-screen.
[FEMALE OPERATOR 10D]
The blizzard seems to be
hindering the feed.
Shall I send reinforcements?
No. That's not necessary.
What about the other E-Pandora?
[FEMALE OPERATOR 10A]
We're currently tracking
Amelia Evans in C-D Block, sir.
She has two Pandora and a
Limiter accompanying her.
[SPENCER] Has anyone in the area
been summoned to subdue them?
That would be Chiffon Fairchild
of West Genetics
and she's already
laying in wait for them.
[alarm sounds]
[AMELIA yells]
I'm afraid that I must
insist you stop.
Chiffon Fairchild.
[RANA] I take it you are
not here as an ally then?
Of course I'm not.
Look, in case you haven't
realized it yet,
this is not West Genetics.
Which means I cannot simply
turn a blind eye to your actions
as I have in the past.
Disarm and surrender
immediately.
Surrender?
You make it sound as if you've
always been holding back.
So try and stop us.
Let's see how powerful the
Unparalleled Monster really is!
Maybe you'll get serious and
wipe that smile off your face.
Well that's too bad.
And here I thought that
I had always shown you
such special favor.
Very well then.
I'll stop you since that's
what you want me to do.
But, unfortunately, this smile
on my face isn't going anywhere.
I mean, after all.
I don't think I'll even
need to get serious.
It shouldn't be too difficult
to defeat all of you.
You can go ahead, Amelia!
Rana and I will
keep Chiffon busy!
[RANA chuckles]
What about--
You've got something more
important to take care of!
[AMELIA gasps]
Thanks, you two.
I can't let her escape!
What is it?
What're you reacting to?
Ahh! I can't
take any more!
The thought of you and me
going at it in sweaty,
hand-to-hand close
quarters combat
is getting me so hot
I think I'm gonna burst!
Uh. How can you even
think of that right now?
[JULIA] Looking at
your body, it's easy!
How 'bout a wager?
Wait, what?
Let's say the winner
of this fight
can do anything they want...
...to the loser.
[CATHY] That's insane!
Scared you'll lose?
Fine then.
I guess I'll just have to
overpower those silly little
Division Waves of yours and
teach you a little humility.
I've have to admit Cathy,
your Quattro Full
Acceleration is first class.
However, avoiding
my Division Waves
is impossible at any
speed below Mach Three.
With you moving so slowly,
there's no way you can win.
Then you're mine.
[CATHY chuckles]
What's so damn funny?
[CATHY] You're relying on old
data and armchair theory,
and not taking
into consideration
the techniques that
I've learned here.
Your provocation
is pointless.
Do you really think
you've learned enough
to defeat me in battle?
Well, since you
don't believe me,
why don't I put it
to the test for you?
Allow me show you
exactly what I've learned
from my battles
with Satellizer!
Initiate Freezing!
[CHARLES] Citroen,
what are you waiting for?
Yes, ma'am!
[CHARLES yells]
[ELIZABETH yells]
Toying with me when
you're powerful enough
to take me down isn't just
annoying it's insulting!
[ANDREI] Her split-images.
If I could just stop them...
[CHARLES] Alright.
It's time to finish this.
[CHARLES yells]
[CITROEN] Aahh!
[ELIZABETH]
She's been frozen?
[ELIZABETH] Andrei!
[ANDREI grunts]
[CHARLES] You're forcing the
activation of your Stigmata.
But that's suicide!
Andrei, you have
to stop this!
[ANDREI] You've got more
important things to worry about!
Forget me!
This is the only
chance we'll get.
So, take her out. Do it!
[ELIZABETH gasps]
[ANDREI] It's okay if I don't
make it out of this alive.
If the last thing I ever
see is you winning,
then so be it. My lady!
Have you lost your mind?!
I can't believe you're
actually willing to let
your Limiter die over
such a meaningless battle!
[ELIZABETH]
How dare you.
You've got no right
to call it meaningless
with all that's at stake here.
I'm fighting to stop
a great injustice.
And Andrei is fighting
because he believes in me.
[ELIZABETH] We will win
even if it kills us!
[CHARLES whimpers]
[alarm sounds]
[FEMALE OPERATOR 10D]
High energy detected.
From these readings, it appears
Elizabeth Mably's attack
has struck
Charles Bonaparte.
[FEMALE OPERATOR 10A]
Vitals fluctuating.
[FEMALE OPERATOR 10B] We need
the video feed for I-T Block,
Area Five back online!
[FEMALE OPERATOR 10A]
Hurry with that status update!
What Pandora ID codes
can we identify?
[alarm sounds]
[SATELLIZER yells]
[SATELLIZER breathes heavily]
How careless of me!
That looked like it
might've hurt you!
[CHIFFON] I can't hold
back when I'm fighting,
and that was just
my first punch,
so think how much worse
the next ones will be.
I hope you guys
surrender before
I end up ripping you
into little pieces.
I'll try to go easy on you,
but I can't make any promises.
[SATELLIZER yells]
[RANA] Do not forget
I am also here!
[SATELLIZER]
Aaaaaahhh!
Oh my.
Your weapon, it just
broke so easily.
[RANA]
As shall you!
Flame Fang!
[CHIFFON]
Aaahh!
I did warn you not
to forget about me,
Miss Student
Council President! Aaahh!
Oh, no, look it
happened again!
I swear sometimes I just
don't know my own strength!
Well, are you ready
to surrender yet?
Perhaps I should stop
you in your tracks too.
What do you think, Satellizer?
[SATELLIZER] Now I know...
why she's called a monster.
Just one attack
and I'm done for!
[RANA]
Pardon me.
[SATELLIZER gasps]
But who was it that you
stopped in their tracks?
[CHIFFON gasps]
[SATELLIZER] Right, we won't
be able to beat her
unless we give it
everything we've got!
You're both releasing
your Stigmata?
[sword clangs]
[squelching]
[CHARLES] I hope you didn't
seriously think you'd won.
Take my advice and
give up already.
Accept it, you've lost.
[ELIZABETH groans]
[ELIZABETH yells]
[ELIZABETH gasps]
[thuds]
[CHARLES] I will admit that your
determination is impressive.
But. In the end, I won.
And do you know why?
I'll do anything
to help my father's
E-Pandora Project succeed.
[FEMALE OPERATOR 10A] Vitals
have gone from yellow to red!
[FEMALE OPERATOR 10C]
Sir, life support functions
are at risk of failing!
[ELIZABETH] What?
Who is your father?
Secretary Marks Spencer.
And I owe him everything.
[ELIZABETH gasps]
[YOUNG CHARLES coughs]
[footsteps]
[beeping]
[MALE DOCTOR 10A] The girl shows
compatibility with the Sacreds.
[MALE DOCTOR 10B]
Look at her overflow numbers.
They're essentially zero.
In my opinion, she's perfectly
suited to be a Pandora.
[MALE DOCTOR 10C] Where did you
find someone so gifted?
[SPENCER] What would you do if
I asked you to become a Pandora?
Would you say yes?
Well, mister.
I'm sorry, I meant
to say father--
I would do...
anything you ask of me!
[CHARLES]
I love my father.
And that love is more important
than your concern
for the E-Pandora.
You'll never beat me,
Elizabeth.
It's been nice knowing you.
[ANDREI] You've gotta
be kidding me.
You think you're fighting for a
cause that's greater than Eli's?
Well then...
I'm gonna prove
why you're wrong!
But it won't feel good!
[CHARLES groans]
That's insane, he activated
his Stigmata even further!
[ANDREI yells]
I'll never let you fall
to anyone, My lady!
[CHARLES groans]
[ANDREI] No matter what happens.
You always get back up!
[ELIZABETH gasps]
[ELIZABETH] Thank you for
reminding me of that, Andrei.
After all, I'm still
Elizabeth Mably.
Even if my body is
bruised and broken.
My heart will never give in.
[CHARLES]
Don't be dumb!
If he keeps this up,
he's going to die!
Ugh! You got some
kinda' death wish?
I'm willing to do
whatever I have to!
I don't care what happens to me.
Only that Eli stops this!
[CHARLES grunts]
Andrei.
Can you keep this up for
another thirty seconds?
[ANDREI]
Yes, my lady.
What's the thirty
seconds for?
I need it for my
Stigma Satellite System.
If it doesn't stabilize
its energy first
it'll create a lag that makes it
hard to hit an opponent.
Thirty seconds is the time
it needs to stabilize,
and line up...
the perfect shot.
You have to stop
this nonsense!
Are you really willing
to risk his life
over a bunch of girls
that you barely even know?
You're crazy!
You told me you'd do whatever
Spencer asked of you.
I assume that means
you're even willing
to risk your life, correct?
Andrei and I are
willing to do the same.
Not because we want
to please a madman.
But for a just cause that's
bigger than ourselves.
We're fighting for the E-Pandora
and that's why we'll beat you.
Volt Longinus Deploy, now!
[CHARLES gasps]
[CHARLES groans]
[FEMALE OPERATOR 10A]
Heart rate dropping!
Vital signs in the red!
[FEMALE OPERATOR 10C]
Medics are being dispatched!
Charles, no.
[ELIZABETH]
You are strong.
But you're also overconfident.
And that is why I was able
to defeat you, Charles.
[ELIZABETH]
Andrei. Hold on, all right?
I'm going to save you.
I promise.
It's too late.
And... it's all your fault.
[ELIZABETH gasps]
He's gonna die
because of you.
This could have been prevented
if you had just given up.
But you kept fighting
and look what happened.
Are you satisfied now?
Of course I'm
not satisfied!
[CHARLES gasps]
What value could there be
in a victory gained
by losing a loved one?
But it was still necessary.
Why do you think
we would continue
to fight despite the
possibility of death?
Why did Andrei keep going
when he knew he might die?
Don't you dare pretend that
you don't know the answer!
Everybody has something
for which they would
risk everything.
Even you.
You're fighting for someone
you hold dear and so are we.
We need to get the medics down
to Charles, on the double.
[JULIA]
Division Wave!
[JULIA] She released
her Stigmata?
[JULIA] And she's faster
than Mach-Three Sonic Waves?
This isn't a Quattro Full
Acceleration anymore!
It's a Quintuple
Full Acceleration!
[JULIA yells]
[JULIA] Do anything
you'd like. Go on.
That was the wager we made after
all and I always honor my bets.
Thanks but I'll pass.
[CATHY] Satellizer,
I've done my part
and now it's up
to you and Amelia.
Good luck.
[SATELLIZER yells]
[RANA yells]
Aaaahhh!
[CHIFFON]
Aaahh!
It would seem...
...that I may need to
revise my nickname.
[RANA screams]
[CHIFFON]
You're both so strong.
Yet people call me a monster.
[SATELLIZER gasps]
You and Rana deserve to be
called monsters more than I do.
[SATELLIZER]
Chiffon...
Are you even human?
No, a Pandora?
It's not really like you to
start asking your opponent
questions in the middle
of a fight, Sattelizer.
But since this will probably be
our last one, I'll answer you.
If you absolutely must know...
I am a true Pandora.
[FEMALE OPERATOR 10A]
Amelia Evans has almost reached
Lab Zero!
[FEMALE OPERATOR 10B]
Three Chevalier reinforcements
are moving in to intercept her!
That's Rattle's!
She's dead and
you will be, too.
So you should just drop
your weapon and give up now.
[FEMALE CHEVALIER 9B]
Unless a miracle happens,
your little rebellion's over.
[AMELIA] In that case.
I'll make one!
[AMELIA yells]
[FEMALE OPERATOR 10A]
Amelia Evans' Nova Form
is accelerating!
Again?
[CHIFFON gasps]
I've been expecting you.
Oh no. What... is this?
[OHARA]
This doesn't make sense!
I created you for the sole
purpose of surpassing Gengo Aoi.
[GENGO] Simple. I'm the head of
Chevalier's inspection team.
[SATELLIZER]
Next time: "Nova Crash."