[yells]
[horn blares]
That's enough!
The winner is Arika Yumemiya.
All right!
[ERSTIN, IRINA laughing]
[YUKARIKO] Arika, Nina,
congratulations to you both.
You two will be the
representatives of the class.
This year, the ceremonial
graduation dance-battle
will be held at the same
time as the inauguration
of the new Fuka Palace.
And so, there will be many
distinguished guests attending.
You must both take heart
not to shame the good
name of Garderobe.
[BOTH]
Yes, ma'am!
[STUDENTS cheering]
[ERSTIN]
Congratulations, Arika!
[ARIKA]
I did it, Ersty! I did it!
[MARIA]
Tomoe Marguerite.
As the runner-up, you will be
the substitute for those two.
Even though you lost,
I trust you will be sure to
keep up on your training.
[TOMOE] Yes, of course.
I understand, Miss Maria.
[ARIKA]
I did it, Sir!
[SERGEY] Is that so?
Antsy made it after all.
[NINA]
Huh?
[SERGEY]
Anyway, good job, Nina- chan .
As always, I'm proud to
call you my daughter.
But the ceremonial dance-battle
is two against two.
That means I'll have to
fight together with Arika,
and when I think about
having to train with her,
it's hard for me
to stay confident.
Don't worry too much about it.
The two of you might actually
make a very good team.
Do you really think so?
But no matter what happens
in this dance-battle,
you must never forget.
You're going to be the Otome
for Grand Duke Nagi.
That is your destiny.
Uh, yes... Of course, Father.
That's right.
Trust me, it's for
your own good.
[YUKARIKO]
It's that time of year again.
Tomorrow, we'll be having
rehearsals for the celebrations.
And next week will be
very busy and eventful,
with the ceremonial
dance-battle,
the graduation ceremony,
and the Meister
ascension ceremony.
The examinations for class
promotions are also coming up.
So to honor Our Lady, I ask all
of you to please do your best.
[STUDENTS]
Yes, ma'am!
Come on, Arika, let's get going.
[ERSTIN]
Arika, want me to help you?
No, it's fine.
I can do it myself.
Arika!
Oh, sorry. I'll be right there!
I'll bring you guys
something to eat later.
Thank you, Ersty!
I can't wait! See ya later!
Wow, gettin' all fired
up about it, huh?
Well, their opponents are
Big Sister Chie and
Big Sister Shiho,
Numbers One and Two
of the Pearl class.
That's why the two of
them have to practice
until really late every night.
I meant you, Ersty, not them.
[ERSTIN]
Hm?
[IRINA]
I mean, come on!
Not only do you bring them food,
but you've taken over some
of their duties too, right?
But that's about all
I can do to help.
And besides, whenever I go
to watch them practice,
they always make me
wanna do my best too.
Right on! Then if you
need anything, tell me.
I'll be glad to help.
Thank you so much, Irina!
Those two sure are working
pretty hard, don't you think?
[TOMOE]
Yes.
Forgive me, Big Sister Chie.
I have been useless
as your room helper.
[CHIE]
Not at all.
Besides, I'm not exactly what
you'd call an ideal Big Sister.
You're really skilled
in a lot of things,
and there wasn't
much to teach you,
so honestly, I feel
like I didn't spend
enough time with you.
And I apologize for that.
That's not true.
However, I think I've paid
close atention to you.
I've always been watching you.
Stop what you're doing.
Big Sister Shizuru
would be upset too
if she found out how you
made Miya do those things.
I'm sorry, Big Sister,
but I have no idea what
you're talking about.
Really?
[ARIKA]
Mmm!
It's so good!
Thank you for everything
you've done, Ersty.
Um... you guys?
I'm gonna do my best!
I've got to, with Ersty
cheering us on!
Then you don't mind
if we increase
our training time, do you?
[ARIKA yelps]
Just kidding!
Sorry about that, Ersty.
What was it you were
trying to say earlier?
Oh... it was nothing.
[NINA]
I see. Well, okay then.
Ugh! Hey, Arika! That was mine!
[ARIKA]
First come, first serve!
[NINA]
What the--? Agh! Why you!
[NAGI]
So that's the whole story.
I'm hoping you guys
can lend us your power.
We refuse.
[RAD] We hear that you
are working with
those despicable cowards
from the Schwartz.
Therefore, we cannot help you.
Aw, and here I thought you
were supposed to be partners
with them at one time.
If you don't mind me asking,
why the messy split?
[RAD]
That is none of your business.
I guess there's no hope, then.
I'll just have to
give up on you guys.
[RAD]
It was a trap.
He knew that we would refuse
to help with his little scheme.
But at the same time,
we can't just sit and watch.
We'll have to make a move too.
[RAD] So you're willing to
stick your hand in the fire?
[MIDORI]
Yes.
I can't afford to keep our
people waiting any longer.
[sighs]
How is Our Lady?
Is she doing well?
Yes.
Preparations are complete for
the Five Pillars Examination.
The production of the new Gems
for next year's Pearl
and Coral classes
is coming along well too.
Also, since Miya has
withdrawn from the school,
I've dissolved her Gem in
special amniotic fluid.
We'll be re-crystallizing
it later.
[NATSUKI]
I see.
By the way, how is
Shizuru doing?
She should be coming
back soon, right?
We ran out of time.
In the end, she wasn't able to
find Smith, let alone catch him.
But the graduation
ceremonies are approaching,
and on top of that, we have to
plan a new course of action
to deal with these
new types of Slaves.
But fortunately,
even though things are
still tense right now,
the situation hasn't
changed all that much.
Now that Fuka Palace
is almost rebuilt,
Queen Mashiro is finally
acting like a real Queen.
If she can continue
to motivate herself,
I'm sure the civilians will have
respect for her once again.
[YOHKO] Let's hope things
will stay like this,
without incident.
[NATSUKI]
Mh-hm.
[MARIA]
In the presence of Our Lady,
we shall now begin the
Examination of the Five Pillars.
[NAO]
Hm.
Oh my gosh, big news!
Big Sister Nao has been chosen
as one of the Five Pillars!
Is she replacing the
vacant Fourth Pillar?
[YAYOI]
Mh-hm!
And not only that,
Big Sister Shiho has been
chosen as the Otome
for King Charles of Florince!
Oh, really? I guess
Cardair backed off!
Probably because of
the whole incident
between Big Sister
Akane and Kazuya.
[YAYOI] Becoming the Otome
for a former enemy country?
It's so dramatic!
Seems more like a
shrewd political deal.
[YAYOI] But since they were
so interested in her,
Big Sister was like
really happy!
Well, I guess as long as
she's happy, that's good.
Oh! What about Big Sister Chie?
Is she gonna be serving
her homeland Aries?
Yeah, although she
is whining about
having to serve under
Brigadier Armitage.
Wow, I'm so envious
of our Big Sisters.
All of them have been
offered positions to serve.
Oh, one more thing!
I heard that Big Sister Shizuru
is coming back soon!
[TOMOE]
Huh?
[LILIE]
Isn't that great, Arika?
She'll be here to see you
when you take center
stage in the dance-battle!
[ARIKA]
Uh-huh!
Now, us normal people
still have an exam to take
so we better'd stop the chatter
and get back to studying.
Irina, I'm having
trouble understanding
parts of molecular biology.
I'm sorry, but right
now I have to run.
I've gotta return this
book to Professor Yohko.
Why don't I return
it for you, Irina?
I have something I need
to ask her anyway.
[IRINA]
Okay, sure! I'd appreciate that.
Hey, Big Sister Nao!
We heard you were
selected as a Pillar.
Congratulations,
you must be proud.
[NAO]
Proud of what?
But this is fantastic
news, isn't it?
It's screwed up my life plans!
They want me to join the
Old Ladies' Military Club?
Like I even care about Our Lady,
or whatever they call her.
[MARIA clears throat]
[NAO whimpers]
Uh, please excuse us.
We have to be going.
Big Sister Nao! Take care!
[YOHKO] Erstin! Do you
know where Irina is?
There's something I have
to tell her right away.
[ERSTIN] Um, I'm pretty
sure you can find her
in the library right now.
[YOHKO]
Thank you.
[ERSTIN] Excuse me, Professor,
but is something wrong?
[YOHKO] That fluid is
extremely dangerous.
If you accidentally
get it on yourself,
it can cause terrible burns.
[TOMOE] I have something
I need to ask her anyway.
Hye, practice felt
pretty good today.
It was all right.
[gasps]
Arika!
Hey, isn't that Ersty?
I've been waiting all
day for your treats!
[ARIKA screams]
[gasps]
[ERSTIN groaning]
[NINA, ARIKA]
Ersty!
Ersty, come on, hang in there!
Thank goodness...
The both of you are okay.
But how did this happen?
Ersty.
Huh?
[ARIKA] "In the end,
I'm still not sure how or why
something like this happened.
But Ersty's burns
weren't that serious,
so that's something
to be thankful for.
Professor Yohko said that if it
had splashed directly on her,
her injuries would've
been a lot worse."
[ERSTIN]
Huh?
Hey, why don't we go
out for a little walk?
[ARIKA]
Uh, sure. All right.
Are you really okay?
Yes.
Thanks to my nanomachines and
because I got help so quickly,
I should fully heal before
the promotion exam.
[ARIKA]
That's good.
The nanomachines
sure are powerful.
I've been thinking about it.
You know, something this helpful
should be shared with everyone,
not just Otomes.
[ERSTIN]
Uh. Yeah... You're right.
[ARIKA] The mysteries of
science... So amazing.
[NINA]
♪ At the window of my heart ♪
♪ stands the profile
of destiny. ♪
Isn't that...?
[NINA] ♪ Oh light that guards
my most secret dreams ♪
♪ shine your power around me. ♪
♪ There's a star
and it talks to me. ♪
♪ Tells me I must
choose just one. ♪
♪ When my loved
one calls to me, ♪
♪ I will transform, with their
voice as the key. ♪
[ARIKA, ERSTIN]
♪ Let me tell of an old story ♪
♪ of a land that
waits to wake. ♪
♪ Let us raise up the
light that shines... ♪
You know it?
It's kinda strange,
don't you think?
You two both know different
verses of the same song.
Yeah! It is sort of weird,
but in a good way.
It feels like some kind of fate
has brought us all together.
Don't you think so?
That can't be possible.
Aww! You're no fun!
[ARIKA chuckles]
[NINA screams]
Damn it! Stop doing that!
--[ERSTIN chuckles]
--[ARIKA] Don't say that, Nina!
[NINA]
Don't ever do it again!
[ARIKA]
Uh, wait a minute!
[NINA]
Hey!
[ARIKA, NINA yelping]
[sighs]
[NINA]
Huh?
Is... that for your patron?
Huh? Mh-hm.
You spelled it wrong, you dope.
[ARIKA]
What?!
Aww...
You know, I really
have to wonder.
Who is this weird guy who's
decided to support you?
I'm thinking of asking
him to come see
the ceremonial graduation
dance-battle we're having.
But that would've all gone
right down the drain
if I had been injured.
Thank you so much, Ersty.
Yeah, I wanna thank
you too, Ersty.
[ERSTIN]
Mh-hm.
Thank you.
It's because of both of you
that I can keep working hard.
And so...
Hey, let's make a promise.
The three of us will definitely
become Meister Otomes!
Yeah.
[ARIKA] "Then the three of us
just stared up at the night sky
without talking
for a long time."
[ARIKA] "I've been able to
meet such good friends,
all thanks to you, Sir.
Oh, I've enclosed
something in the envelope!
A handkerchief that
I embroidered myself.
I worked really hard on it
and I hope you like it.
Wave the handkerchief
during the dance-battle,
and I promise I'll see you.
After that, please
allow me to meet you.
I wanna say thanks in person.
It's the least I can do after
all you've done for me.
To my dear Sir. From Arika."
The day's finally come.
I'm so relieved we're able
to welcome this day with
such beautiful weather.
I think it's a good sign.
[NATSUKI] I want to thank
all of you for your assistance.
Miss Maria, Miss Yukariko,
and of course, you too, Shizuru.
[SHIZURU]
Hm.
However, it is a
bit of a shame.
It seems that this year
most of the nations
have sent representatives rather
than members of royalty.
Well, that can't be helped,
considering the world's
in such disarray.
It doesn't bother me.
At least this way, we'll have
fewer things to worry about.
[PEOPLE cheering]
Remember, to this day, no Coral
has ever beaten a Pearl.
So just think of this as
a simple test of skill,
and take it easy.
I will definitely win!
For your sake, Father.
Ha. Okay. I understand,
Nina- chan .
[ARIKA]
Huh?
[SERGEY]
Oh, hey, Antsy.
What are you doing here?
[SERGEY] I received an
invitation asking me
to come observe
this dance-battle.
[ARIKA]
Hmph.
Well, just be sure to try hard
to not be a burden for Nina.
Stop mocking me!
I'm definitely gonna
become a Meister Otome!
My patron will be watching too,
so I'm fighting for him!
I see. You're probably right.
This "patron" of yours,
he must be watching over you.
Uh, Father?
[NATSUKI]
I expect a dance-battle worthy
of this year's graduation,
so please try your hardest.
[ARIKA, NINA, SHIHO, CHIE]
Yes!
I am gonna be reborn
along with this new castle.
Hey, and don't forget,
Arika, it's a race.
[ARIKA]
Mh-hm.
Nina, good luck to you too.
Even though it was
only for a short time,
you were my first contract.
Do your best.
[NINA]
Yes!
[meows]
[PEOPLE cheering]
[NATSUKI] Now, as part of this
year's Garderobe graduation,
we'll begin the
ceremonial dance-battle.
What are you doing?
Calm down and focus.
I'll take this chance
to do my maki-makis!
Red maki-maki, blue maki-maki--
Stop that.
Go for it!
Do your best!
Ugh. Who really cares what
happens here? I sure don't.
[MASHIRO]
My fellow citizens!
Before we begin
the dance-battle,
I would like to unveil my
restored castle for you,
the brand new Fuka Palace.
[applause]
[MASHIRO] I now wish
to make a declaration!
With this castle,
we will usher in a new and
brighter era for our country!
[MASHIRO]
Huh?!
[PEOPLE chattering]
Huh? That's nothing like the
castle in Mashiro's drawing.
What horrible taste.
[MASHIRO] Wh-What is that?!
I never authorized that design!
N-No! I never--
This isn't my castle!
It's moving. What is that thing?
My castle's supposed to be...
Now, let's get started.
No way!
And fire.
[gasps]
Those things...
[NINA]
Things are looking bad.
[ARIKA]
What'll happen now?
[MIKOTO meows]
[ARIKA]
What?!
[MIKOTO meowing]
[ARIKA]
You're kidding!
[NINA]
You understood that?
[ARIKA]
Not a bit.
[MIKOTO meows]