[MASHIRO]
Hasn't Mikoto woken up yet?
Afraid not. She's still
sleeping like a baby.
She's got such a happy
expression on her face too.
It's kind of annoying.
[MIKOTO sighs]
I can't eat any more... Mai...
[MASHIRO]
How can you be so calm?!
Do you know how long we've
been stuck on this island?
By now they've
probably gone started
the Strategic Otome
Limitation Talks without me!
Not to mention all the work
that'll be waiting for me
in Windbloom.
And there's Arika as well.
Right now I...
What's wrong?
Nothing!
Why would I care about that
inconsiderate little brat?
Ugh.
At any rate, we have
to get off of this island
and back home as
fast as possible.
[MAI]
That's true,
but it's not as if we can
swim all the way back.
Why don't we just
sit back, relax,
and wait until we can
find some other way?
[MASHIRO sighs]
[MASHIRO] Arika, if you're
planning to come, then hurry up.
What's taking you so long?
[NATSUKI]
Now that we're assembled,
we shall proceed with the
first meeting of SOLT,
the Strategic Otome
Limitation Talks.
[YUKINO] Chairwoman,
I wish to submit a request.
While I do agree that the
Otome question is important,
I believe we have a much
more pressing issue
that should be discussed.
We have to decide what to do
about the mysterious being
that attacked
Windbloom and Aries.
[NATSUKI] Looks like this
is going to be a long day.
I'm counting on you, Nao.
We've come to the right
place, no doubt about it.
These have gotta be
those ancient ruins.
[CHIE sighs]
[CHIE] Oh man, I've been so cold
lately that this water stings.
And it hurts even more
when I think about
the President and the
Headmistress cooped up
in that meeting
looking all serious.
Well, we can't attend
ourselves anyway,
considering the main
objective of the meeting
is to discuss eliminating
the use of Otomes.
It's too bad, really.
Hey there, Antsy.
What's bugging you?
Why don't you relax
and enjoy yourself?
[ARIKA]
How can I relax
when you're constantly following
me around, Big Sister Mahya?
When I'm changing,
or taking a bath,
even when I'm going
to the bathroom!
Of course I'm following you.
I can't have you
wandering around
and getting involved in
another bus-jacking.
Hey, those are the
Headmistress's orders,
and I'm stickin' to 'em, okay?
But I can't stay here!
I've gotta go find Mashiro!
How come?
I thought you had a big fight
with Queen Mashiro.
That's true. It did happen.
But still!
What will you do when
you find her? Apologize?
Or are you planning to
make her apologize to you?
[CHIE] Why don't you leave
her alone, Big Sister Mahya?
You know, Arika, everyone
else is worried too.
Big Sister Shizuru,
Her Majesty, and Miss Maria.
Even the Brigadier.
But right now, we have no
idea as to what we can do,
or what we should do.
At times like these, we need to
rest and refresh our bodies.
That's one of our
duties as Otomes.
--[AKANE, KAZUYA yelp]
--What are you doing?
I told you, you're not to come
within three meters
of each other!
B-Big Sister Mahya!
Emperor Kazuya,
what were you thinking?
You might be nothing more
than pretty window
dressing for the throne,
but you should still
maintain your dignity!
[KAZUYA grumbles]
Come on, Big Sister Mahya,
you're not being fair to him!
Kazu's doing his best!
Oh really?
Then why don't you stop
trying to do it with him
every time you see
an opportunity?
[KAZUYA]
Akane...
[KAZUYA yelps]
[SHIHO] Oh, dear.
You haven't changed since
our school days, Akane.
You're still a
brazen seductress.
To think you're the Meister of
my home country's Emperor
makes me so embarrassed!
Oh, I think I might
cry from the shame!
Huh?
Come on, not you too, Shiho!
[ROSALIE] Hey, I know a way
that will make everyone happy.
Akane can get married to Emperor
Kazuya and become Empress,
and you could leave Florince
and become the new
Meister for Cardair.
[ROSALIE chuckles]
A brilliant idea,
if I do say so myself.
Oh really?
I didn't realize that
you were that desperate
to have me leave my
position in Florince.
Could it be that the "returner"
is jealous, Big Sister Rosalie?
Oh my goodness! Can we say
"persecution complex"?
Maki-maki Shiho.
[growls]
[chuckles]
[yells]
What in the world's
your problem?!
How dare you trip me! Hm?
Well this place was sure
built on the cheap.
[laughs]
It's divine punishment!
Rosalie!
I'm gonna maki-maki
you to death!
[gasps]
[screams]
And just where do you
think you're going, Arika?
Hey! Give that back!
[MAHYA]
No way!
[ARIKA]
Wait! Big Sister Mahya!
Mahya, come on!
Please, I need that back!
Oh, you poor little
girl, all vulnerable.
Why don't I cover those
up for you, Arika?
[ARIKA whimpers]
[ARIKA screams]
[ANH chuckles]
You're so cute and perky,
just like your breasts.
[ANH chuckles]
Big Sister Anh! What are you--?
Aoi, I really hope
I'm wrong about this,
but is that alcohol?
[AOI]
Huh? Yes.
This is bad.
[ANH]
Come on everyone!
We're taking a bath, aren't we?
So what do we need swimsuits
for? Let's get naked!
No! You can't do that!
[LAULA] She's right, Big Sister!
Not here, at least!
[ROSALIE] It will upset your
father, Emperor Nguyen.
You guys are no fun
at all! Ha-ha!
[SHIHO, MAHYA, ROSALIE,
CARLA screaming]
I'm not giving them back!
Kazu, you pervert!
Wait, Akane, you've
got it all wrong!
[CHIE groans]
Big Sister Anh gets outta
control when she drinks.
And when it comes
to her behavior,
well, let's just say
she's a bigger sister
than Big Sister Shizuru.
[ALL screaming]
[ANH]
Come on, the bottoms next!
[NAO] You sure are
a strange one, Nina.
You know, you wouldn't have
had to follow me all this way
if you just gave me that
diary to begin with.
I can't. Not this.
[NAO]
Hm.
Okay.
This is my turf now.
And that means whatever treasure
we find is gonna be mine.
[NINA]
Hm.
I can see that you haven't
changed at all, Big Sister Nao.
Hey, now that I'm a Pillar,
I've gotta start saving
for my retirement.
A girl's gotta get
her money somehow.
Anyway, if you don't
wanna hand that over,
then I'll be counting
on you to lead the way.
After all, Sergay's the only
person who's ever been here,
besides Nagi.
All right.
[NAO] So, what's the
first trap we're facing?
[NINA]
Let's see...
According to this,
there's a trapfloor
immediately after you enter.
[NAO]
What, that's it?
Who would ever fall for
a stupid trap like that?
[click]
[BOTH]
Huh?
[NINA]
Uhh...
[BOTH screaming]
Yeah. We're currently in
recess at the moment.
It's rough going,
just like I expected.
I see.
I guess we've got no choice
but to wait for Nao and Nina.
Is there any change with
Shizuru and the others?
Negative. We're still
monitoring them.
We can definitely
detect signs of life,
but other than that, nothing.
[NATSUKI]
I understand.
Professor Gal,
have you heard anything from
Midori and the others yet?
[GAL]
Nope, no news yet, I'm afraid.
Our leader and Rad,
uh, I mean Reito,
are still out searching
for the Black Valley.
[sighs]
Let me know when they
get back to you.
[GAL]
Roger.
[IRINA]
Oh, wait, Headmistress!
There's something else
that's worrying me.
It's about that
plant-like thing
that's still covering the
Predecessor's Mausoleum.
The part that's above ground
seems to have stopped
growing for the most part,
but the roots underground
are still spreading
at a steady rate.
[NATSUKI]
That doesn't sound good.
How many surrogate
system cores remain?
[YOHKO]
Three.
If we push it, I might be
able to give you four.
[sighs]
If the situation gets any worse,
I'll return there myself
to try severing it again.
Keep watching over it till then.
[IRINA]
Yes, ma'am.
It's hard to handle this sort
of crisis without you, Shizuru.
[gasps]
I fell, didn't I?
The diary!
[NAO]
Relax, I've got it right here.
[NINA gasps]
[NINA]
Big Sister Nao!
When did you get so
out of shape, Nina?
[NAO, NINA screaming]
[NAO] If you give me too much
trouble, I'll leave you behind.
I guess you read it then.
I didn't want anyone else
to read his diary.
Not even you, Big Sister.
Of course you didn't.
This entry's interesting.
"Tomoe Marguerite
visited me today,
and gave me a pin-up
magazine as a gift.
Nina is a model in it.
I realized how much
she had grown.
I couldn't hide my
surprise and happiness.
Unable to control myself--"
Please! No, don't! Stop it!
I can't read another
word of this.
[NAO] By the way, Nina,
are you still a virgin?
[NINA] What?! Where'd a
question like that come from?
[NAO]
Heh. I guess you still are.
Even without his memories,
Sergay's still lame
in some areas.
And that must mean the
surviving nanomachines
are still squirming around
inside your body.
Ugh, you make them
sound disgusting!
And another thing!
Sergay is not lame, okay!
[NINA yelps]
[ARIKA sighs]
The meeting has
certainly been going on
for a long time, hasn't it?
[ARIKA] You already brought
all of Mashiro's luggage.
[AOI] It's our job to make
the necessary preparations.
After all, Miss Mashiro
might be back at any time.
[yelps]
[ARIKA]
Mashiro, how could you?!
I thought we made a promise
that we'd build a nation
where people will smile
from their hearts!
That's exactly why I'm doing
what a queen needs to do!
Why won't you
understand, Arika?!
How could I understand
something like that?!
If you won't understand,
then just shut up and
follow my orders!
Mashiro...
[AOI]
Miss Arika?
[ARIKA groans]
Look at what you found there.
So if you're still a virgin,
then which of you
is holding back?
Is it you? Or Sergay?
Well, you see...
The new Sergay is kind,
and I love him.
But he's not the man
I used to call my father.
That man is still...
Well, he's inside this diary.
The Sergay of the past,
he's still in here.
To tell you the truth,
I didn't want to read this.
It was too painful.
But then I heard about everyone,
about Arika, Queen Mashiro,
and Big Sister Shizuru...
...and all I could think of
was Arika's sad face.
That was what gave me
the courage to read it all.
[NINA] You could say
that this is my treasure.
Your treasure?
[NINA]
The days I spent at Garderobe,
and the world my father
risked his life to protect...
Even though all I can do
is stand aside and watch,
I can still believe
that Arika and her Big
Sisters will protect it.
And even if it's just
a small thing,
if I can make up for all the
things I've done, then I...
Please, you gotta stop it.
This is way too boring.
Just like I thought,
you haven't changed a bit.
Well, neither have you.
[NAO chuckles]
[AOI]
Keep this a secret,
but whenever Miss Mashiro
has to travel,
she always brings
that drawing with her.
It's the first thing
she packs ready to go.
She always tells me that it's
her most important treasure.
[ARIKA]
Let's make it a race.
We'll see if I become
a Meister first
or you become a queen first!
How about it?
But I'm already a queen!
Uh... then...
how about a queen
that will bring happiness
to everyone in her country?
Good idea!
Okay! The race is on!
Mashiro...
[MASHIRO]
I see.
You're worried about
all your friends
back in Windbloom, aren't you?
[RIBBON]
Uh-huh.
This mountain is a special
place for all of us.
[MASHIRO] The Black
Valley is supposed to be
the lifeblood of the
Schwartz, isn't it?
[RIBBON] But we won't
fight anymore, right?
[MASHIRO] You mean
Windbloom and the Schwartz?
[RIBBON]
Yeah.
There's nothing to worry about.
Both sides have been working
very hard over the past year
to improve our relations and
establish lasting peace.
[RIBBON]
Oh! That's great.
[RIBBON gasps]
[RIBBON]
Come over here, Your Majesty!
[RIBBON mumbling]
Uh, not to be rude,
but what are you doing?
[RIBBON]
I'm making a wish at the Shrine
of the Queen, of course!
I'm praying that
this mountain and I
can return to our friends soon.
Oh, I see.
I'd bet good money that
this is the last door.
[NINA]
What is this?
This feels like
a major discovery.
But there's no way
we're gonna be able
to carry that out of here.
Is that all you're
worried about?
[NAO]
Of course it is.
Jeez.
Looks like this stuff
isn't worth anything.
The Headmistress said that
aside from the data,
I could grab whatever I wanted.
Big deal.
The Book of Neptune ?
[gasps]
Big Sister Nao!
[NAO]
Just give me a minute, okay?
[NINA screams]
Nina!
Huh. So there's a watchdog
guarding the treasure, then.
It's so pathetic though.
It makes me wanna cry.
Big Sister Nao! Above you!
Wait a minute. That looks
like the Pure White Diamond!
So this must be the thing that
got Shizuru and the others.
Big Sister, don't you think
we should get outta here?
Are you kidding?
We can't leave yet.
I haven't found any
treasures to sell.
I am the Fourth of
the Five Pillars,
the Break String Spinel,
Juliet Nao Zhang.
I seek authorization via
the surrogate system.
Materialize!
What's that? Nao's fighting?
Would you get out of here?!
You're not an Otome, so you
won't be able to do anything!
But I--!
[gasps]
I'm not letting you get away!
Outta my way!
[NAO]
Huh?
[NINA]
I won't let you do that!
Don't draw attention
to yourself, you idiot!
[groaning]
[gasps]
No!
Big Sister Nao!
[screams]
[screaming]
No way...
That thing...
[YUKINO] There are more of them
appearing all over the world...
If they all hatch together...
...this world's finished.
[RIBBON]
Your Majesty, you got one!
[MASHIRO]
Uh?
[MASHIRO yelps]
[MASHIRO]
Come on!
[RIBBON]
You can do it, Your Majesty!
Whatever this thing is,
it's gotta be enormous!
[RIBBON]
Come on, Your Majesty!
Hang in there!
[yells]
[rumbling]
[MASHIRO]
Uh?
What the heck is that?!
Nina?!
[NATSUKI]
Our final episode is next,
so I'll give you all a chance
to say what you want.
[ARIKA] I'm gonna combine
my powers and transform!
[MASHIRO]
The world is finally at my feet!
[NINA] I want a love
scene with my father!
[MIKOTO]
The Miroku Army arrives!
[MAI] The key to victory lies
in my special ramen noodles!
[RIBBON]
Um, I...
[ERSTIN] I wanna survive
to the end this time.
[ARIKA, NINA, MASHIRO, NATSUKI,
MAI, MIKOTO chuckle nervously]