[CONTROLLER A]
Typhon One is approaching
along its predicted trajectory.
Recalculating mass
using topospatial radar.
[CONTROLLER B] Current error
divergence is plus 0.03.
Now updating all data links.
No change in planned
mission order.
Where is the attack team?
[CONTROLLER C] They've just
passed Space-One velocity.
They'll be arriving at the
attack point any second now.
It's about time
we finished this!
I'm gonna crush that hemorrhoid
into itty-bitty pieces!
It's an asteroid--
[SARA] It's called an asteroid,
Big Sister Haruka.
You're supposed to be
the mission leader.
Could you at least
try to act like it?
[HARUKA]
Hmph.
[MASHIRO]
Arika...
This is quite an
emotional moment.
I never thought I'd
live to see the day
when all nations would be
working hand in hand
towards a common cause.
It wouldn't be possible
if it weren't for you,
Headmistress.
After all, you were the one that
gave us Garderobe's technology.
[NATSUKI]
Not really.
It was a matter
of a good timing.
Right after this Karakawa
Observatory opened,
it was able to detect
the incoming asteroid.
If it crashes into the ground,
it won't only be Aries
that's destroyed.
It would demolish at least six
of the surrounding nations.
Hey, Mai!
Is it okay if I have
one of these snacks?
No, they're offerings.
You can't eat them yet.
[CONTROLLER A]
Ten seconds to firing point
for the Meteor Breakers.
Jettison the Force Wings.
Hereby commencing
Meteor Breaker Ignition.
Those rocks!
Don't worry, they'll burn
up in the atmosphere.
Got it!
[CONTROLLER A] Seven, six, five,
four, three, two, one, fire!
[yells]
[CONTROLLER B] Abnormal vector
change detected for Typhon One!
It's fallen out of orbit!
[CHIE] Adjust the path
of the Meteor Breakers!
[CONTROLLER B] It's too
late! They're gonna hit!
[CONTROLLER A]
The alignment has shifted!
A large piece remains!
It's accelerating as a
result of the explosion!
It's entered the atmosphere!
Its current course?
The projected point
of impact is...
...Windbloom!
We're going after it!
[SARA]
It's no good, Big Sister Haruka!
Send up the second attack group.
[HARUKA]
An attack grope?!
[YUKINO]
She said, "group," Haruka.
[HARUKA]
Arika?!
I'm gonna try to stop it!
Mashiro, the contract!
Right!
Blue Sky!
[CONTROLLER A] Meister Arika's
reached her ultimate form
with Materialize Zwei!
She's chasing after the debris!
[CHIE]
She's fast.
What's this, "Materialize Zwei"?
It's a special ability
unique to Meister Arika.
We're still investigating
its characteristics.
It's like the late
Blue Sky Sapphire.
Does that mean Arika
can use the same powers
that were possessed
by her mother?
Yes, but more than that.
It's more accurate to say
that this is the true form
of the Blue Sky Sapphire itself.
[ARIKA]
I have to protect everyone!
She's passed it!
Come on, Arika!
Akatsuki!
[yells]
The Blue Sky Sapphire...
She collided head on
with Typhon One.
[ARIKA]
This is Arika Yumemiya!
Repeat, this is Arika Yumemiya.
The asteroid has been
totally eliminated.
Well then, the
mission's complete.
Arika...
Uh! Did you see me,
Mashiro? I did it!
I protected the
world for everyone!
[gasping]
[ARIKA grunting]
Ow, that hurt...
[meow]
[ARIKA]
Hm?
Huh? What the--?
Was... Was that a dream?
[MARIA]
Really,
what sort of dream
were you having
that made you end up like this?
[ARIKA]
Huh?
Miss Maria?
What? Miss Maria, was
that all just a dream?
I thought there was an asteroid,
and I made it go boom!
No, you weren't dreaming.
As you can see, you really are
the saviour of this planet.
[ARIKA]
Huh?
Oh, thank goodness.
It wasn't a dream then.
Yes, you may be a Meister,
but unfortunately you lack
the required number of credits.
That means you are still a
student under my supervision.
So, Arika Yumemiya,
first, run 50 laps
around the palace.
When you finish I want
you to open your copy
of What It Means
to be an Otome ,
and transcribe
chapters 12 through 15.
Yes, Miss Maria!
Uh! Aww...
[MARIA]
Dismissed!
[ARIKA]
Uh, right!
Uhh...
Hello, Meister Arika.
Is there some sort of problem?
Oops, sorry! Uh, I mean...
Please excuse me.
Honestly...
Now, what's the next item?
[SAKOMIZU]
Huh?
Oh, yes. Moving on, the next
topic on the agenda is "SOLT",
the Strategic Otome
Limitation Talks
to be held next month
in the nation of Artai.
Right. Mikoto! Let's get going!
[ARIKA]
"Dear Nina,
I don't know where you might be,
but I hope this letter
reaches you!
I wrote it from my heart,
like I always do.
It's already been a whole year.
The city has calmed down,
and everybody is
doing really well
in their day-to-day lives now.
Mashiro's been
working so hard lately!
She's becoming more
and more like a queen.
I don't know much about
that kind of stuff,
so I can't really
help her with it,
but I'm studying hard
and doing my best
so I can become a great Otome!
If you ever feel like it, Nina,
please come and
visit us someday.
I'm sure that by then,
this country will be a place
where people can smile
from their hearts!
I can't wait to
show it to you..."
[ARIKA]
Huh?
[WORKERS shouting]
[SERGEANT A] Everyone,
please disperse quietly.
You're forbidden from protesting
outside the palace gates.
Don't give us that!
We're just exercising
our workers' rights!
[WORKER B]
Let us in to see the queen!
[WORKERS shouting]
Come on... Get going.
[GAL] Your inventions still need
that extra push, don't they?
Professor, I'm wondering,
is this really the
extent of all the damage?
[GAL]
What?
This crater that was made
by the falling meteor--
[GAL]
It's still unknown,
and that's why we have
to study it more, okay?
[NATSUKI] "The proposal to
abolish the minimum wage
and benefits law is close
to being approved.
The workers' union of Wind City
has been holding strikes."
Oh, boy, looks like
Queen Mashiro's rule
will face one
hardship after another.
[yelps]
Shizuru.
It looks like the queen
is facin' some opposition.
Still, considering the current
situation in Windbloom,
I think she's been makin'
the right decisions.
Me too.
But on top of all that,
we've got those Otome
Limitation talks next month.
I can already tell
that's going to be
another big headache for us.
--[whooshing]
--[BOTH] Huh?
[BOTH grunting]
Hello, Headmistress!
We just finished collecting
all the samples.
[GAL] Now, let's head back
to the school, shall we?
Irina, what is a
researcher like you
doing riding around on the back
of a professor like that?
That goes for you too, Professor
Gal. You should know better.
Director, our sample recovery is
complete and we're coming back.
Is that all right?
I'm sorry, but could you check
out one more place for me?
Oh, wait! Leave that
where you found it!
I just need you to see
if the ruins are there.
If that's all then, I can go
by myself and take a look.
Natsuki, you go
back ahead of me.
Sure, if you don't mind.
Thank you.
All right, in that case...
We must defend ourselves against
the enemies of the Academy.
For now, let's fall
back to Garderobe!
Why can't she just simply
say "We're going back"?
[GAL]
Who knows?
[MASHIRO sighs]
I know we have
them all the time,
but these meetings
are exhausting.
I think you've been doing
a splendid job Miss Mashiro!
I'm very happy and proud of you.
What about those people
holding the sit-in?
Yes, I'm afraid
they're still out there.
Huh... I see.
Mashiro!
[MASHIRO] What, you're
asking about that now?
No, I'm not going to repeal it.
It's part of a necessary reform.
Why? Whaddya mean?!
A lot of people could
get their wages cut!
How could you do
something like that?
[MASHIRO] Don't worry,
that's not gonna happen!
Why else do you think
I've been having meetings
every single day?
I haven't been doing it
for fun, that's for sure!
[ARIKA]
I know that.
But all of them are worried
about what's going on.
You haven't been talking with
those protestors, have you?
Yeah, of course
I talked to them!
[ARIKA]
Mh-hm, mh-hm. Mh-hm.
You're such an idiot, Arika!
Huh? Now you're
calling me an idiot?!
Why won't you listen to
what they have to say?!
I feel sorry for them!
I'm not doing this
because I want to!
You can't dictate the
policies of this country
by how sorry you feel!
[ARIKA] You've changed
a lot lately, Mashiro.
[MASHIRO] The problem is,
you haven't changed one bit.
My, that's rather strange.
It's a lot different down here
compared to that other crater.
I wonder if it's supposed
to be that way.
Huh?
[MIYU]
Run, Bewitching Smile Amethyst.
That creature...
[SHIZURU]
Hm?
[gasps]
[ARIKA] What's with her,
trying to act so mature?
Grandma always told me
that you can stand on
your toes all you want,
but that doesn't make
you a grown-up.
Sounds to me like you're
feeling lonely, Arika.
After all, it's like
you're being left behind.
[ARIKA]
That's not true!
Aw, come on, Arika,
don't get upset.
Just accept the facts!
But that's not the way it is!
[pop]
[ARIKA]
Huh?
[GAL]
Oh! Your face is very cute!
Ugh! And if that wasn't enough,
today Mashiro's gone
off on her own!
Hey, Miss Cat Goddess,
are you a food expert?
Yeah, are you?!
[WOMAN A]
Look, it's the Cat Goddess!
Can I take a picture of you?
Good day to you, Cat Goddess!
[MIKOTO chuckles]
[MASHIRO] Ugh! That Arika
is so annoying sometimes.
I put a lot of hard
work and energy
into getting that act passed.
She has no idea!
Huh? Then the two of you
ended up having a fight?
N-No, we weren't
having a fight!
It's not like we're children!
[MAI chuckles]
Mai! Come on,
where's my bowl of ramen?
It's almost ready.
Mashiro, just don't get
too emotionally involved
and rush blindly ahead.
You tend to see what's only
right in front of you.
But I'm not getting
emotionally involved at all.
[RIBBON] Sorry for
the wait, Your Majesty!
One bowl of Cat Goddess ramen!
It looks delicious!
[RIBBON] Yours is coming
right up, Cat Goddess.
The soup is still really hot,
so please be careful.
[MASHIRO]
What a great waitress!
[RIBBON]
Enjoy!
By the way, Mai,
what's happening with the
disarmament of the Slave Lords?
Well, since Garderobe has
its hands full right now,
they haven't had the
time to come and help
all of these people.
I see.
So even a little girl
as cute as her
still has to carry
the burden of a Slave.
That's awful.
[MAI]
Your ramen's getting cold.
Yeah, I know that.
Is that the debris
from the big meteor?
That's right.
We're analyzing the materials
and studying its composition.
There are some things
about it that worry me.
[ARIKA]
Really, how come?
Remember?
There was that
weird course change
that the Admiral and the
others were talking about.
Uh?
[NATSUKI]
Irina?
Shizuru hasn't returned
to Garderobe yet.
Has she contacted you at all?
[IRINA]
No.
There's been nothing from
the Gem transmission
or the heavy particle link.
[GAL] I guess she must've
found a pretty girl
along the way to distract her.
Ugh. Professor.
[IRINA, YOHKO chuckle]
I'll give her a call.
Come in, Meister Viola! Hello?
Huh?
[MASHIRO sighs]
Thank you very much.
Mai! Another bowl!
No way, Mikoto. You've already
had more than enough.
[RIBBON] If you eat any more,
you won't have room for dinner!
Right.
[whines]
[MIKOTO]
Huh?
[MAI]
Hm?
Falling asleep right after
eating? That's a little weird.
[RIBBON]
Sleepy-sleepy?
Do you wanna have nap-time?
[PEOPLE gasping, shouting]
[IRINA] Let's see, Big Sister
Shizuru's current location is...
What is it?
Her Gem's not reacting
to our scans.
I don't know what to make of it.
[GAL] I'm getting nothing
on my end either.
[alarm blaring]
What's wrong?!
Your Majesty, over there!
[RIBBON]
I'm scared!
[IRINA] A reaction to a
higher-order element? Amazing!
But it's not coming
from a Robe or a Slave!
Then what in the world is it?
[GAL]
Hey! Everyone, look at this!
[ARIKA]
It is a Slave!
[IRINA] Oh no! Isn't that right
in the center of Cat God Park?
Garderobe has no record
of this creature.
It could be a new type of Slave.
Contact Fuka Palace, Director.
Arika, I'll take
you straight there!
Right, okay!
Sakomizu, mobilize the
entire Windbloom army
and release an emergency
warning throughout the city.
And where's Arika?
What did you say?!
Come on, wake up, Mikoto!
Hey, Mikoto! Mikoto?
[RIBBON]
Wake up!
Authorize the contract!
[SLAVE LORD A]
Meister Mai!
[SLAVE LORD B] We'll assist
you with our Slaves!
No, don't. You should leave
the fighting to us Otomes.
[SLAVE LORD B]
But...
Take the Cat Goddess to
the top of the mountain.
[SLAVE LORD B]
Yes, ma'am.
[SLAVE LORD A]
Good luck!
[RIBBON]
Go get 'em!
Materialize!
[MAI]
Evacuate the city!
It's Meister Mai!
It really is her!
The Tragic Meister!
[groans]
How much longer are they gonna
keep calling me that? Jeez!
Don't worry about me.
Evacuate the tourists!
What do you want us to do
with this cat, Your Majesty?
[ARIKA]
Mashiro!
[MASHIRO]
Arika!
Where have you been?
Have you been goofing off again?
I could ask you the same thing!
You're the one
who snuck out here
to have ramen all by yourself!
Shut up! I only came
out here because of you!
Would you two cut
it out already?
Honestly, this is no time
to be having a fight!
[PEOPLE screaming]
Mashiro!
We'll argue about it later.
I command you,
release your powers,
and use the strength
of the Blue Sky.
Materialize!
[PEOPLE cheering]
Blue Sky!
I'm counting on you, Arika.
[NATSUKI clears throat]
[MASHIRO]
Uh?
Oh. Oh, yes.
Headmistress, of course,
I'll need assistance
from Garderobe as well!
Well, if you insist,
I suppose I can help out.
Load Chrome Cartridge!
[ARIKA yelling]
What the--?!
Arika!
[yelling]
[gasps]
Ugh. What is this thing?
No way!
That Slave just totally defeated
Arika's Bolt from the Blue!
Director, how are we gonna
deal with this thing?!
I really don't know.
If it's a Slave,
then there should be a Slave
Lord somewhere nearby.
[alarm blares]
Ugh. What is it now?
[GAL]
Intruders!
They've broken into
the tomb of the Otomes!
[IRINA]
Oh no... but that's...!
They've taken the
Pure White Diamond,
And now they're heading
for the Predecessor's room!
[MARIA]
I'm on my way.
Calm down, Irina.
Materialize!
What's happened here?
Our Predecessor?
How dare you deface this
place in such a manner.
It's unforgivable!
Show yourself, whoever you are!
Hm?
It's you...
[IRINA gasps]
[IRINA, GAL]
Huh?
[IRINA gasps]
Professor Yohko!
The reaction level for Lady Fumi
is dropping really quickly!
At this rate, the Headmistress's
contract will--
Go to emergency mode!
Switch the authorization
system to that right away!
Wait, do you mean--?
Yes, over there.
[IRINA]
The Surrogate System?
[yelps]
What? The Emergency Mode?
What's wrong, Headmistress?
The contract system
has been switched over
to the new surrogate.
After what happened in the past,
we decided to build a
backup for emergencies.
Director, what's
happened? Report!
There are intruders!
We received a warning
from the mausoleum,
and lost reaction from Our Lady.
Uh!
We even lost contact
with Miss Maria
when she went after them!
Please return
immediately, Headmistress!
Someone's invaded the
Predecessor's room.
What? But who?
[ARIKA]
Headmistress!
There are people
stuck over there
that weren't able
to escape in time!
You have to go and
save them, quickly!
Headmistress, I want you
to return to Garderobe.
Wait, Mashiro! Saving those
people has to come first!
Otome still maintain
peace in this world.
We can't risk another incident
like the one with Nagi!
Yes, I understand.
Arika, I'll leave it to you.
[ARIKA]
Mashiro, how could you?!
I thought we made a promise
that we'd build a nation
where people will smile
from their hearts!
That's exactly why I'm doing
what a queen needs to do!
Why won't you
understand, Arika?!
How could I understand
something like that?!
If you won't understand,
then just shut up and
follow my orders!
[gasps]
[groans]
Why did it fail?
Please give the power of
the Blue Sky to my Otome!
Give back her power!
Are you all right, Arika?
Why did I...?
Hey, Mai!
What is it?
[NATSUKI] Yohko! What's the
location of the intruders?
[YOHKO]
I don't know,
but in the meantime, the
subsystem has reached its limit!
Huh? What is that thing?
Just to let you know, this'll
probably only work once.
Okay!
[ARIKA] I can do this
without Mashiro's help!
[yells]
We did it, Arika! Nice job!
Yeah!
[thunder rumbling]
Arika...
[NATSUKI]
Mai! Arika!
The Predecessor's been
attacked by unknown forces!
What?!
Be very careful.
Whoever those bastards are,
they also took the
Pure White Diamond
from where it was sealed.
Wait, are you saying?!
[screams]
Mai!
Arika!
Huh? What's going on?!
Oh no, Mashiro!
[ARIKA]
Mashiro!
Arika!
Mashiro?
Mashiro!
[MAI] Oh my gosh, we're finally
releasing an OVA, Arika!
[ARIKA] Yeah, Mai!
At last, our own OVA!
[MASHIRO] Do you even
know what OVA means?
[ARIKA]
Of course!
It stands for, "Outrageously
Voluptuous and Attractive."
[MASHIRO] I can see you
still have no intention
of taking these
previews seriously.