Queen Mashiro!
[CROWD screams]
Everyone! Run! Go!
[ARIKA grunting]
Wow!
No way!
[YAYOI]
Amazing...
Get out of here! Hurry!
[CROWD screaming]
[ARIKA whimpering]
[ARIKA screams]
[HARUKA]
Hey, Coral!
Great job holding on so long!
Isn't she from Aries?
Continental Orb Topaz!
You got a tight
future ahead of you.
Haruka, I think you
mean "bright future."
All right, Coral, listen up.
An Otome needs three things.
Strength, skill, and guts!
They're not done?
Hurry up!
Please, Arika, try
and calm down.
But I don't know
what's gonna happen!
So how am I supposed to
be calm at a time like this?
It's not possible!
The council has
made its decision.
Please come in.
Well, then, it's time.
I shall now announce
the council's verdict.
Before you do so,
I have a favor to ask.
[SERGEY]
Huh?
[NATSUKI]
Go ahead. What is it?
[NINA] I would like the
opportunity to face this girl
in a dance-battle again.
I want to have
a decisive result.
That is something
I cannot allow.
Besides, if it
still matters to you,
you will have many chances
for a rematch in the future.
Rematch? You mean...?
First, Nina Wong.
We have deemed you the
winner of the dance-battle.
All charges against you
have been dropped.
As for you, Arika Yumemiya,
due to your efforts
to prevent casualties
and your display
of skill and potential,
this committee has decided
to grant your special request.
Uh... So that means...?
We accept your enrollment.
[ARIKA]
Thank you very much!
I'm really, truly grateful!
Thank you so much!
If you want to thank someone,
you should really
thank those two.
The others were
stubborn, like Princess--
No, Queen Mashiro, I should say.
The one who helped
convince them
is the President
of Aries Republic.
Her Excellency, Yukino Chrysant.
Well, it was Meister
Haruka who told me
that you have the makings
of an excellent Otome.
All I did was report
that to everyone else!
[HARUKA]
Hmm...
Oh! What the...?!
What are you...?!
[screams]
[HARUKA] Looks like she'll
need a lot more training.
This is the President
Yukino's Otome,
Meister Haruka Armitage,
the Continental Orb Topaz.
You make sure you learn
everything you can
at this academy!
You've got a lot of potential.
I know, because I say so,
and I'm never wrong.
[ARIKA]
Right!
Please do your best!
We shall be taking
our leave now.
[NATSUKI] Thank you for your
assistance, Your Excellency.
And your help was
appreciated too, Haruka.
I wasn't doing it for
you or the headmistress.
To become an Otome,
you need energy!
And I sense a lot
of it in this girl.
Well, you certainly
haven't changed!
You and I still
have a battle to fight!
You'd better get practicing
if you hope to beat me!
[SERGEY] Well, I'm
pleased with the decision.
[NINA]
Yes.
I'm sorry to cause you trouble.
Not at all; in fact,
it was rather fun!
Work hard and become
a great Otome!
Well, it seems that
things have ended up
exactly how the
headmistress had hoped.
I don't see a problem.
For the time being.
After all, we didn't
lose anything.
Or are you beginning
to have a few doubts
about that girl, Arika?
No, sir.
I don't have any doubts.
[NAGI]
Hmph.
Well, whatever.
But she certainly is a
very interesting girl!
It seems that every
time I leave our country,
I run into all sorts
of interesting things.
Like the worshippers
of the Black Valley.
So I'm thinking
it will be a little while longer
before I go back home to Artai.
[SERGEY]
Huh?
[MASHIRO]
Damn that President of Aries!
She puts on an honest
and quiet face,
but she ends up manipulating
everyone with pretty words!
I hate people like that!
I am supposed to be
the queen of this country!
But my castle is still
in that wretched state,
and nothing is going
the way I want it to!
Miss Mashiro?
What is it?
I'm sorry to rush you,
but you must go over
these documents
submitted for your approval.
You see,
the various ministries
can't continue their work
without them.
That uniform is proof of
being a student of Garderobe.
Keep that in mind,
and wear it with great care.
[ARIKA]
Yes!
Arika Yumemiya,
you are about to become
a student at this academy.
But first, there are some things
you must be informed of.
All Otome must abide
by certain regulations
as well as observe
several restrictions.
One of them is that
you must always abstain
from any relationships with men.
The nanomachines are the
source of an Otome's power,
but they are vulnerable
to Y-chromosomes
and a type of serine protease
called prostate
specific antigen,
both found in males.
If you get either of
them into your system,
your nanomachines will dissolve,
and your body will build
complete immunity against them.
You would never possess
the power of Otome again.
In other words,
if you fall in love with
a man and marry him...
Or... do a few certain
other things with him,
you will lose the power
of the Otome.
You must remember this.
Oh.
[NATSUKI]
There is one other thing.
If you become a Meister Otome,
that is, become
a full-fledged Otome
who serves a master,
you must remain by
your master's side
and share your life force
with theirs through your GEM.
[NATSUKI] If you are hurt,
your master will be hurt.
And if your master dies,
you will die too.
[ARIKA gasps]
[NATSUKI]
To give up love,
relinquish a woman's happiness,
and devote your life
to your master.
That is what it means
to be an Otome.
Tell me.
Are you prepared for that?
Yes!
Then, Arika Yumemiya,
in the name of the
source of all Otomes,
our great ancestor,
I grant you this Coral GEM,
proof of your candidacy
to become an Otome.
I'm Arika Yumemiya! And, um...
My dream is to become a
really cute and cool Otome!
It's nice to meet all of you!
[YUKARIKO] Arika, your
seat number is number 51.
You will attend classes
starting tomorrow.
Good luck, and do
your best to move up
the class rankings, okay?
Right!
Now then, Nina,
Erstin, please stand!
--Yes, ma'am.
--Uh, yes.
I have a favor
to ask of you both.
[ARIKA]
Wow, what a beautiful room!
And the view is great!
This is super cool!
[sighs, giggles]
I guess we'll be seeing
a lot of each other, uh...
Huh? Oh, I'm Coral
number 17, Erstin Ho.
It's nice to meet you, Erstin!
This'll be fun!
I will agree to
share a room with you,
because the
headmistress orders it.
But I have no intention
of being cozy with you.
How mean!
And here I was thinking
we were all friends
in the same class!
[NINA]
Friends?
Every student in this school
is competing with each other
to become an Otome.
Your classmates are not friends.
They're rivals.
Rivals, huh?
What do you think, Erstin?
Is everyone like that here?
Uh, well... yes.
I suppose so.
You see, only one out of
two Corals can graduate
to the Pearl Class.
And only a handful of those
can become a genuine Otome
and receive the rank
and GEM of a Meister.
But this is the first
time I've ever seen Nina
get so tough and say
anything about a rivalry.
She acts serious
most of the time,
but she's also very nice.
[ARIKA]
Hmm...
Well, that's fine!
I'm going to do my best anyway!
And one day, I'll beat Nina
in a head to head battle!
Once again, you've gone farther
than I would have thought.
I am sorry, Miss Maria.
However...
I understand.
I was as surprised
as anyone to see
the Blue Sky Sapphire again.
But that...
...is a separate issue entirely.
Garderobe Academy
must treat every student
from every country
equally and with fairness.
A girl without
family or sponsorship
will have a difficult time.
I think you
understand that well.
[door closes]
[NATSUKI sighs]
So you decided to put them
both in the same room together.
Natsuki, you sure are mean!
You're not one to talk, Shizuru.
Those two will encourage
each other's growth
by being rivals.
They will be like you
and Haruka once were.
And also like me
and my old roommate.
[NATSUKI] First the
Slave Lords of Schwartz
use creatures to attack
Wind Kingdom,
and now we have the
cyborgs of the Black Valley
to deal with as well.
[SHIZURU]
Aswad.
The mysterious military unit,
active behind the scenes since
the War of the Twelve Kings.
[NATSUKI] Otome can't always be
merely the flowers of society.
We'll need those two
to become much stronger.
That may be so,
but before we worry about that,
I think there's a more immediate
problem for us to solve.
[NATSUKI]
You're right.
If I had known something
like this would happen,
I would've provided
some sort of a scholarship.
[NATSUKI]
This isn't good.
Oh, wow! A feast!
Looks delicious!
Did Nina and the others
really make this themselves?
But I can't really be happy.
Why? What happened?
You're, uh...
Irina.
Irina Woods.
We're in the same class!
Nice to meet you!
Here, one of the teachers
just gave me this.
Let me see.
Tuition... costs of
school materials...
...and other fees,
for a grand total of...
What?! That's a lot of money!
Which means I have
to find a way to make
some money really fast!
Mmm, this is delicious!
You're paying it
all by yourself?
[ARIKA]
Of course!
You mean you two don't?
I'm here on my
country's scholarship.
My homeland Aries is
taking care of all my fees.
And in my case, my
parents pay for everything.
You're lucky!
I don't have any family,
and I don't know
anyone who'd support me.
[YAYOI]
No way!
[ERSTIN] Ah! This is
Lilie, Yayoi, and Miya.
They're students in
Star Class, too.
What was that "no way" about?
Well, um, we were
just talking about Arika.
It's unheard of for someone
to enroll here midterm.
Besides that, you seem to
know Queen Mashiro personally,
and Big Sister Shizuru has
been watching over you too,
hasn't she?
[YAYOI] So we were just
guessing a little!
We thought you might
have some rich sponsor,
or maybe you're
a royal princess.
No, no, it's not
anything like that!
I don't even have any
family after Grandma died!
Oh, but my mother
should still be alive!
At least I think so...
Then why'd they
accept someone like you?
[TOMOE]
That's enough, everyone.
You shouldn't bombard her
with so many questions.
You're making
Arika uncomfortable.
Hello. I am the Number Two
Coral, Tomoe Marguerite.
I'm the student representative
for the Star Class
at this school.
If there's anything
you need to know,
please don't hesitate to ask.
Thank you, Tomoe!
It's nice to meet you!
[slurping noise]
Huh?
What are you doing?!
Hey!
Aww! And it's brand new, too!
Are you all right?
That's Queen Mashiro's cat.
It's been wandering
around the dorms recently.
Ah, you don't have to do that!
It'll come out in the wash,
and I have another one!
[TOMOE]
Don't worry, I don't mind.
Stupid cat!
The pet has problems,
and so does the owner!
[sneezes]
Attention!
Big Sisters 1 through 12
have gone to the baths.
Girls on room-duty
should come quickly!
Is it that late already?
Big Sister will lecture me!
Forgive me,
but I have to go now.
'Kay!
Thanks again!
We should get going too.
[ARIKA] Oh, Erstin, you have
that "room-duty" thing as well?
What is it, exactly?
Mmm... Well...
We're the Coral students who...
...take care of our Big
Sisters in the Pearl Class.
[CHIE] Hm... So it's not
as if that girl is here
representing a country, then?
They say she's from the
border of Freedom Nation,
and she doesn't have
any relatives either.
Accepting her will make
people doubt the dignity
of our academy!
Dignity?
As always,
you tend to worry about
the most trivial things, Shiho.
Excuse us, Big Sister Chie,
may we wash your
back for you?
Ah, yes. That would
be much appreciated.
All in all,
I do not approve
of that girl's enrollment
in our academy.
[AKANE]
Why not?
Isn't it obvious?
No matter how you look at it,
she'll never be fit
to be an Otome.
[AKANE chuckles]
Well, I think she
has potential.
How can you?
She not only fought
a dance-battle,
but she held up that
plane from falling
even though she'd never
worn a Coral Robe before.
No normal girl
could manage that.
You and I are gonna
have to work extra hard.
We don't want our underclassmen
to surpass us, do we?
[SHIHO gasps]
Seems to me they're
already surpassing you
in a few areas.
[SHIHO yelps]
[CHIE laughs]
Uh, is anyone here?
Uh... All full.
Oh, well!
I'll just wash it tomorrow.
[NINA]
♪ At the window of my heart ♪
♪ Stands the profile
of destiny ♪
♪ Oh light that guards
my most secret dreams ♪
[SERGEY]
Hey, what are you looking at?
I-I'm so sorry, Father!
I didn't mean to.
I just wanted to borrow
a red pen, and then I found...
Are you curious?
That person...
She was my dream once.
A long time ago,
when I was the same age
as you, Nina- chan .
[NINA] ♪ With their
voice as the key ♪
[NINA]
"My dream"...
You went out again
without permission?
[NAO]
Yes, and what about you?
You shouldn't be copying me,
even if you are my
room-duty helper.
You do want to become
a great Otome, right?
I'm hoping you'll
keep earning points
and serve our country
in my place.
You don't have to
worry about me.
Well if that's
the case, Nina,
maybe you shouldn't
spend so much time
worrying about
that Arika girl.
I'm not... worried.
She certainly caused
a lot of fanfare
by enrolling in this school.
Well, whatever.
It's nothing to do with me.
Besides, she might
be crushed very soon.
[ERSTIN] You can use
my bed tonight.
You'll probably develop
a lot of fevers
for awhile after
putting on your GEM.
Ow. It's hot.
It feels like...
...like starting right now,
I'm gonna be reborn.
[ARIKA squealing]
So cool!
I'm gonna be an Otome!
You can bet on that!
The duty of the
Otome is one of honor,
and dedicating her life to
serving nobility like me.
How could a worthless little
thing like you be of any use?
[NINA]
I beg the council...
Allow me the chance
to fight against this girl!
Besides, even if
you somehow win,
you'll be crushing
the dreams of Nina,
who has endured strenuous
training to enter the academy.
Is your dream really
worth that much to you?
My dream?
[NATSUKI]
To give up love,
relinquish a woman's happiness,
and devote your
life to a master.
That is what it means
to be an Otome.
Tell me...
Are you prepared for that?
It's all right.
I can do it.
This is the dream
that I found, after all.
Can you see me, Mother?
[HARUKA]
My time has come at last!
Starting next episode,
I'll go wild with
my Otome powers!
[YUKINO] But you're not
in the next episode!
[HARUKA]
What?!
I was gonna use
my exciting moves
and teach that new girl
a thing or two!
[YUKINO] I think that's
why you're not in it...