[NGUYEN] My condolences
regarding the youngest daughter
of the Ho family.
I never figured that
the whole family
was working for the Schwarz.
I was careless.
[NATSUKI]
Your Majesty...
However...
I can understand what the Ho
family must have been feeling.
[ANH]
Miss Natsuki.
I'm sure that you
know this by now:
many of the Otomes in the
past came from that family.
And during the War
of the Dragon King,
they lost many of
their female relatives.
I do understand, Big Sister Anh.
However, if Nagi sets the
Harmonium into motion,
this world will be
thrown back to the age
of the Dragon King War.
No, even worse, back to the days
of the War of the Twelve Kings!
We must prevent that
from happening at all costs!
For this reason, Your Majesty,
I ask you to please
lend us your power.
You really have grown to become
quite impressive, Headmistress.
Th-Then...
Yes. The nation of Annam will
follow the terms of the treaty
and aid Garderobe
as best we can.
Thank you very much,
Your Majesty.
[meows]
[REFUGEES chattering]
Don't worry.
Yes, there's still lots left,
so hold your horses.
Here you go, son. Eat up.
Thank you so much.
[MASHIRO]
I see. So the five of them left.
[VILLAGER 22A]
Yeah.
They went to deliver our message
of retribution to Cardair.
Leader...
Hey. What's that over there?
[MASHIRO] Don't tell me
they've returned already!
[VILLAGER 22A]
No, it's not them.
I don't like the looks of this.
[VILLAGER 22B]
Hurry! Prepare for an attack!
[BOTH gasp]
Wait a minute, isn't that...?
[ARIKA]
Sergey...
[SERGEY]
Attention, citizens of Aswad.
I am Major Sergey Wang
of the Imperial Military
of Artai Principality.
We have no intention
of fighting with you.
Our only purpose
here is to pick up
Queen Mashiro of
Windbloom Kingdom,
along with the Otome
accompanying her,
Arika Yumemiya.
We ask that you turn
those two over to us
as soon as possible.
Your deadline is noon.
Have them come to
the Dragon's Cemetery.
If they are late,
we will be left with no choice
but to discontinue
our peaceful relations.
I trust you will make...
Hey, what are you doing?
They're gonna see you!
[MASHIRO]
A-Arika!
[SOLDIER 22A] Sir! A message
from the Valkyrie Unit.
"We will begin
our plan shortly."
[NAGI]
I see.
[SOLDIER 22B] We have
a report from Mister Smith.
"Our insurance has awakened."
[NAGI]
Really?
Insurance?
Yes, that's right.
It's someone who may know
the final verse to the song.
[NINA]
Huh?
[NAGI] Our search team
found her at the bottom
of the valley, barely alive.
She's the one person
who is closest to Mashiro.
[MASHIRO] I'll leave these
people in your capable hands.
All right. Sure thing,
Your Majesty.
Arika.
It'll be fine. Come on,
let's go, Mashiro.
You know this has
to be a trap, right?
But we still have to go.
[meows]
[LUMEN]
There they are.
Looks like the Otomes from all
the nations have gathered here.
[LUMEN] Mm. Even the Lovely Onyx
is making an appearance.
It looks like
they're ready for us.
[RAD] This fight might be
a bit tougher than we thought.
[MIDORI] But we're still goning
to push through and defeat them.
[RAD]
Yeah.
Let's go.
--[humming]
--[SERGEY] Huh?
I knew it. I knew
you'd come here.
Are you all right?
[gasps]
[SERGEY]
I'm assuming Queen Mashiro
is hiding somewhere close by.
That shows good judgment.
You always have
to be cautious...
...when you're facing the enemy.
[gasps]
[ARIKA]
I don't understand.
Why did you have
to be my patron?
Why did you support me?
And what about that time...?!
That was because you...
[SERGEY growls]
I should stop making excuses.
It was probably because...
I was... because I was
attracted to you.
Even I was surprised by myself.
After all, you're the
same age as Nina.
But I admit, I was deeply
attracted by that brilliant
smile of yours.
To the way you looked ahead
and chased after your dreams.
I was drawn to you and
your determined eyes.
That's why, when the time came,
I betrayed the Grand Duke,
and tried my best to save you.
It was the first time I'd
ever done anything like that.
But... the result of that was...
How's... Nina?
She's fine. On the
outside, at least.
But, looking at her
now hurts me.
And so that's why...
I have a duty to take care
of the mistakes I made.
As a soldier of Artai...
and also... as a father to Nina.
[ARIKA]
I feel sorry for Nina.
[gasps]
[ARIKA]
I...
I think...
I probably fell
in love with you, too.
I loved you.
That's why I understand how
Nina feels about you, Sergey!
[growls] I know that!
I've always known!
But then, why?!
It's not something logical.
Nina... is my daughter.
But, Sergey!
[SERGEY]
So right now...
...as her father, I have to do
whatever I can for her sake.
That is how I can
express my love for Nina.
[ARIKA]
Mm.
I was hoping that
you'd surrender.
But I suppose you'd rather,
keep chasing your dreams, right?
[ARIKA]
Hm.
That's the Antsy I know.
[grunts]
Ugh.
[gasps]
Are those Slaves?
[grunts]
[yelps]
[ARIKA grunting]
Arika!
What?! No way!
Princess Mashiro
should be hiding
somewhere around here. Find her.
Roger that.
[NAGI] You've memorized
the song, right?
[NINA]
Yes.
I can't believe it.
I really must be the
luckiest guy in the world.
All that's left is
for you to test it out.
If I do, then Father--
I mean, Major Wong--
won't have to go through
with his plans, will he?
You don't have to worry
your pretty little
head over that.
I already told the Valkyries
before they left that
they had to watch over Sergey.
I'm sure they'll be keeping
a close eye on him.
And, if the song is real,
then we have no more use
for Mashiro or Arika.
We only needed them for
their verses of the song.
So if you truly wish to,
you can kick them both off
of the stage, permanently.
Arika?
Yup.
Hasn't she always been
a nuisance to you?
[gasps] Well...
You certainly are a kind person.
[NAGI]
But I'm afraid that kindness
will only bring you pain.
Since, from now on,
you'll be using this.
[TOMOE laughs]
Hello, Arika.
It's been a long time since
we've seen each other.
I'm glad to see that
you're doing well.
[ARIKA] Tomoe, that Robe
you're wearing...!
Isn't it wonderful?
It's a Meister Robe that
Grand Duke Nagi gave to me.
It's just like Big Sister
Shizuru's Robe.
It doesn't need
a Master to be used.
It's a Robe that lets me
feel free and extraordinary.
Hey, Arika.
Please allow me this dance.
I'm so excited, I think
my heart is about to burst.
Because the truth is, since
the first time I met you...
...I have always hated you!
[grunts]
[ARIKA, TOMOE grunting]
[ARIKA yells]
It's an even battle
against a Meister Robe.
This thing really does have
awesome power... but...
[screams]
But this is what happens
to you if you try
to go against the plans
they've set for you. Figures.
[gasps]
It's okay. I'm fine.
I can't fight with her;
I can only watch her from afar.
In which case, the least
I can do is endure this pain
so Arika can continue the fight.
[meowing]
What's wrong, Mikoto?
Why? Why am I
the one to play it?
Do you really need to know?
[NINA]
Uh...
Oh! Finally, the Harmonium...!
First, the Protector.
[gasps] What? My Robe...
[NAGI]
Then, the player.
--[singing]
--[gasps] This song...
[VOICE]
♪ ...following to an end ♪
It's the lullaby...
But these lyrics...
I've never heard them before.
It's a fourth verse?
[VOICE] ♪ The shooting star,
it drifts away ♪
♪ And the time of
rebirth draws near ♪
You!
[SERGEY]
That's enough!
A-Arika.
Stop resisting and
surrender peacefully.
[meowing]
No way! Even Big Sister Chie...
This fight is now over.
Arika!
You don't have to
worry about me, okay?!
If they had any
intention of killing me,
they would've done it already!
Listen!
As Master and Otome,
both of our lives are the same!
If one of us gives up,
then we both do, and it's over!
Mashiro...
[TOMOE laughs] How wonderful
the two of you are.
Faithful and true,
to the point of foolishness!
[ARIKA grunts]
[yawns]
[gasps]
[NAO screams]
Why did you stop like that?
[NATSUKI]
Look.
Huh?
[gasps] That's...
--[CARDAIR PEOPLE screaming]
--[RAD grunts]
[OTOME 22A yells]
Let me first commend
you on putting up
an impressive battle.
But I fear that,
to fight on, would only be
a waste of your time and mine.
You cannot defeat me.
[MIDORI]
Hah. How about proving that?
Here I come!
[BOTH grunting]
[yells]
[grunts]
[FIAR]
Prepare yourself!
Gakuten-oh!
Huh?
[screams]
If you want revenge against me,
then wait for me in
the World of the Stars.
[FIAR]
Damn it...
Emperor!
It's impossible...
Fiar's been... defeated...
[ARGOS groans]
[NATSUKI]
I don't believe it.
Cardair Castle has fallen.
How did this happen?
If this is their idea
of a welcoming party for us,
I'd say they've gone overboard.
--[thud]
--Huh?
Then that stuff with Miya...?!
That's right.
That piece of trash
only followed my orders.
I was the one who planned
everything from the beginning!
The uniform, the swimming pool,
and the survival test.
Why would you do such things?
[gasps]
[ARIKA grunts, yells]
[ARIKA groans]
[TOMOE] You see, Arika,
it's because Big Sister Shizuru
always had her eyes on you.
It annoyed me so much.
That's why I wanted
you to disappear.
But that bothersome
Erstin got in the way.
She was such a foolish idiot,
but she was also rather lucky.
[gasps]
Oh, but I heard she died!
That's a big relief.
I would never have
been such a coward.
I'll get everything I desire.
Wealth, status, honor, my Big
Sister by my side--everything.
Using this power of the Otome!
[ARIKA]
I won't forgive you.
You have no idea...
what Ersty...
...went through...
You have no idea!
Huh. You're so stubborn.
You can still move
after that? Oh well, then.
Let's go, Lee, Nobue, Jeanne!
Let's do it! Dance of Valhalla!
No! They're really
trying to kill Arika!
Arika!
[screams]
[TOMOE groans]
Look... Wh-Who the hell is that?
[CHIE]
Isn't that...?
[gasps]
[ARIKA]
Miyu...!
Please excuse me
for being late, Arika.
You're the person
from that night...
[MIYU]
The "Cursed Black Diamond."
The accursed Gem
of the Valkyries.
You people would play
around with the corpse
of Lena Sayers in order to
create these abominations?
[gasps] Her corpse?!
The most important order left
by that person is up to me.
I must destroy you people.
You...!
A cyborg's sword won't beat us!
I'll show you what we can do!
[MIYU] Unlock Numbers
Four through Twelve.
Set anti-materializer
output at 50 percent.
[TOMOE yells]
[TOMOE]
My Element!
[gasps]
[SERGEY grunts]
Wait, Miyu! Don't!
Nina, you can use
this thing to do
whatever you want!
So, what is it you
wanna do right now?
[SMITH]
So beautiful!
At last, this is the power
of the legendary Harmonium!
[SMITH gasps]
What happened?
Did we just travel
through time and space?
Well, there seems
to be a floor. Look.
But more importantly,
it's this place...
Sergey!
I apologize for this.
I believe I avoided
critical areas, but...
[groans]
[gasps]
[MIYU]
Arika, be careful.
It's coming.
[ARIKA]
What is it?
How come there's a
thunderstorm all of a sudden?
No... That's not a thunderstorm.
Oh, no... Don't tell me...
It's the Ultimate Black Diamond.
Nina...
Ah...
Nina... it's you...
Hello, Father.
[gasps]
Father! You've been wounded!
[sighs] Nina...
Arika... But why...?
[NINA growls]
[NINA]
Arika... It was you again!
Nina! It's not like that!
Please, Arika,
you must stand back.
[ARIKA]
But...
No, Nina! Stop this!
I won't forgive you.
I won't forgive somebody
who hurts my father!
Never!
[MIYU]
Sword Marie.
Begin the higher order
materialization sequence.
Miss Alyssa,
grant me your power!
[MIYU] Confirming hereditary
information of Alyssa Sears.
"Artemis: the golden sword."
Mission start.
[screams]
[BOTH grunt]
[ARIKA grunts]
[ARIKA]
Huh?
[gasps] Wha--?
[ARIKA]
What?
[TOMOE] Isn't this Robe
simply wonderful?
[MIYU]
No.
[TOMOE] I'm so excited,
my heart is about to burst!
[MIYU] Your small chest
doesn't show it.
[ARIKA] Miyu! You
shouldn't be so honest!
[MIYU] I understand.
Oh, you're beautiful.
You have such a nice body.
[TOMOE]
I'm going to kill you for sure!