[CROWD shouting]
[SOLDIER A]
The rebels! They've broken in!
[SOLDIER A] Over there!
They're entering from this side!
[MAN A] They've reached the
king's room! Somebody! Anybody!
[SCHWARTZ MEMBERS] God of
ancient light, knowledge,
and wisdom. Grant me
your loyal servant.
[roars]
[SOLDIERS shouting]
[SERGEY gasps]
[MINISTER]
The princess isn't here!
Find her! Find her!
[RENA pants]
[RENA grunts]
[sighs]
You must live.
[grunts]
[RAD] Is this already the
limit of your strength
without the power of the Otome
and the Blue Sky Sapphire?
[RENA gasps]
[RAD shouts]
[ARIKA grunts]
[CROWD chatters]
Yet another failed lead.
Still. I always knew
that finding her
wouldn't be an easy task.
[CHILD A]
Over there! Kurochs!
[CHILD B]
Kurochs?!
[SERGEY]
Kurochs?
[CHILD C] Hey mister,
there's something over there!
[SERGEY] Don't worry, son.
It's just a bit of trash.
[CHILD 1C] It is not!
It's a big piece of trash!
PASSENGER A]
So these are Kurochs!
PASSENGER B]
They're the real thing!
[KUROCHS chirp]
They say that seeing a Kuroch
is a sign of good luck.
What kind of good luck?
Such as meeting a
beautiful stranger.
What are you saying, Handsome.
[ARIKA]
Huh?
[grunts]
Aw. I thought they'd
stop and rescue me.
[gasps]
[ARIKA] Hey, wait for me!
Come back here and save me!
♪
[WAITER A]
Pardon me, miss.
You are the number one ranked
Coral student, Nina Wong, right?
[NINA]
Excuse me, I didn't order this.
[WAITER] It was sent by
the customer over there.
[NINA]
Huh?
To the future Otome.
To the beautiful Otome.
[CROWD]
To the Otome!
[NINA gasps]
Uh...
Water...
[grunts]
Huh?
Thank you very much for
the drink. I am honored.
[gasps, groans]
[BOTH yelp]
No!
[BOTH grunt]
Ah!
[NINA grunts]
[CROWD chatters]
Nina! What happened?
[NINA grunts]
[gasps]
F-Father?!
Nina- chan ... your legs.
[NINA]
Uh...
[screams]
[NATSUKI]
I've had a bad feeling lately.
[SHIZURU] You have a
very good reason to.
After all, next week is
Princess Mashiro's coronation.
There may well already be a few
unwanted guests in Wind City.
You mean the Schwarz?
They know full well that our
pact with Wind Castle
prevents us from
taking any action.
That means they're
bound to try something.
After all, it's been 14
years since that incident.
And after all this time,
we still haven't found "her".
That is why I have requested
your return, Shizuru.
It's all part of the job
for the Fire Pillars.
We're expected to help
out the school.
And Garderobe Academy is still
in an a very awkward position.
Well, in any case, we have
no choice but to see
what happens and
react accordingly.
I'll be counting
on your help.
You forget that it's my job to
help you with all your problems,
Headmistress Natsuki.
[gasps]
[CHILDREN chatter]
[ARIKA]
Hm?
Hm...
[NINA]
Please forgive me, father,
for embarrassing myself in
front of so many people.
Don't worry about it.
It was just an accident.
An unlucky accident, Nina.
You're right, Father! Unlucky.
[ARIKA]
Um...
[NINA gasps, growls]
Well... I, uh...
Oh right! Here you go!
And thank you so, so much for
the juice earlier, Nina- chan !
[NINA grunts]
Nina.
[ARIKA]
Huh?
It's Nina.
The only person who can call
me "Nina- chan " is my father.
Uh, your father? Hm...
Why is that?
Dunno.
[TATSUHIKO]
Major!
[SERGEY, AKIRA]
Huh?
Ha! I hope your trip to the
home country went well, sir!
[SERGEY]
Hm.
Thank you for coming to
pick me up, Nina- chan.
Yes.
And as for you...
I've been trying to think
what you remind me of,
and I finally remembered.
You are Antsy!
I'm Antsy?
Mm-mm! Don't call me Antsy!
My name is Arika!
Arika Yumemiya!
[chuckles]
Well, pardon me.
I'm an officer at the Embassy
of the Artai Principality.
the name's Sergey Wong.
I hate the name Antsy,
And I hate people
who call me Antsy!
[NINA] I think it
suits you. Antsy Arika.
Wait! I owe you for the juice!
[NINA]
Don't bother.
Hey!
I can't just leave it like this!
Grandma always told me
to pay my favors back!
You can do that by going away.
You're annoying,
you're an eyesore,
and you're bothering me!
Huh?
Hey! Hey, Nina!
God, you're noisy.
Stop screaming my name so--
[gasps]
[NINA grunts]
[giggles]
So awesome!
[gasps]
[ARIKA]
Hey, what is this thing?
[bell rings]
[ARIKA]
Wow! A real train ticket!
I'd better keep it safe.
Uh... I brought
along some water.
Want some? Here!
Stop it.
You're embarrassing me.
Aw. Nina, are you
angry about something?
Would you please,
please stop talking?
[ARIKA whimpers]
Huh?
[gasps]
[ARIKA gasps]
It's a castle!
That's where the
princess lives, isn't it?
What's she like?
I don't know.
The coronation doesn't
happen until next week.
[ARIKA]
Huh...
[SOLDIER B]
Princess!
[SOLDIER]
[AOI]
Your Highness! Your Highness!
Princess! Your Highness!
[AOI sighs] The princess
has gone missing again.
I've already sent several search
teams to look in the city.
[AOI]
Thank you for helping, again.
[BOTH sigh]
[MIKOTO meows]
[ARIKA gasps]
[NINA] Well, that's it.
I have to go now.
Hey! Hey, wait up!
Wait for me, Nina!
[ARIKA exhales]
Hey!
I'm very sorry, but from
now on, you are on your own.
As you can see, I'm very busy.
[ARIKA] Um, I'm looking for
the way to Garderobe Academy.
Do you know it?
[NINA gasps]
What do you need at the Academy?
[ARIKA]
Well, I'm looking for my mother.
But the only thing I know about
her is that she was an Otome.
So I thought, Garderobe is
a school for Otomes, right?
So, then, if I
become an Otome too...
[NINA]
Impossible.
Why's that?
You really don't
know anything, do you?
Where do you come from?
Galelia.
Huh. I don't know what kind
of backwoods place that is,
but you don't understand
anything about being an Otome.
[ARIKA whines]
Hm?
Hey, hey, hey! What is that?
Television!
[ARIKA gasps]
Television?
Windbloom is a place where
the old technology of Earth
is still preserved and used.
[ARIKA gasps] Oh my gosh,
is that the princess?
[NINA]
No. "That" is an Otome.
She is Meister Shizuru.
Wow, she's so pretty!
Mei... Meister?
Huh? Nina!
[ARIKA sighs]
Hey, what's this thing?
[NINA]
A hologram.
[ARIKA]
Huh...
Wow, that too?
[NINA]
Yes.
[ARIKA] This is awesome!
It's like magic!
[ARIKA exhales]
So, that's a hologram too?
[sighs]
They are all hologram--
[NINA]
Huh?
[MAN B gasps]
It'll be a hundred years
before you catch up to me!
[MEN gasp]
[MASHIRO shouts]
Move!
[ARIKA gasps]
[MASHIRO screams]
[NINA grunts]
[NINA]
She... passed me?!
Grab it!
[NINA grunts]
[MASHIRO screams]
[MASHIRO grunts, screams]
[MASHIRO groans]
Well that was suicidal. Huh?
[NINA grunts]
[ARIKA grunts]
Who are you guys?
Y-you did well!
I commend you.
--[footsteps]
--[ALL] Huh?
You there!
Return the girl at once!
[MASHIRO yelps]
Listen to me, you two!
You must save me!
These people are nothing
but evil kidnappers!
[ARIKA]
WHAT?!
[BOTH gasp]
[ARIKA]
Oh, no!
These must be the outlaw people
Grandma always warned me about!
Let's go!
Wait! We're only here to--
[gasps, grunts]
[ARIKA, MASHIRO pant]
[yelps]
Stop!
--[MASHIRO yelps]
--[ARIKA grunts]
[MAN D]
Wo-- Woah!
[NINA, MAN D grunt]
[MAN D grunts]
Wow, Nina, you were amazing!
Hey, where did that girl go?
Uh, Hm? Hm?!
[MASHIRO mumbles]
[ARIKA]
Uh, oh.
[SAKOMIZU]
She got away?!
You stupid idiots!
Next week is her coronation!
The princess must have
done this because she knew
it was her last chance to
get away. Right, Mikoto?
[MIKOTO grunts]
Well, seems like we're safe now.
Oh. Oh, really?
[sneezes]
[ARIKA]
Wow! What is this place?
[NINA]
It's the old airport.
[ARIKA]
Airport?
[MASHIRO] You really don't
know anything, do you?
It's the place where
flying machines stay
and rest their wings.
[ARIKA] No way! This thing can
fly in the air like a bird?
That's amazing!
[sneezes]
Ugh, I am soaking wet here!
Go and get me some dry clothes!
Here you go!
Not that! It's dirty!
[ARIKA] Hm. That's not nice,
considering I saved you earlier!
Grandma always said if
you don't show gratitude,
you'll get it in the end.
What? How dare you!
I'm leaving.
[MASHIRO]
What?!
You seem safe now.
You're on your own from here.
Wait a minute! Are you just
going to abandon me here?
[scoffs] I need to get
back before curfew.
Well then, take a look at this!
[gasps]
Then, you are...
You people call yourselves
"the flowers that
serve the royalty."
So hurry up and
start serving me!
Kneel!
[NINA]
Please forgive my impoliteness.
[ARIKA]
Huh?
Nina, you don't have to
apologize to a brat like this!
[NINA grunts]
[MASHIRO] You really don't
know a thing, do you?
She is merely doing her duty.
As an Otome of Garderobe,
she is required to obey me.
Huh? An Otome?! Then Nina...?
Under the contract of darkness,
I fulfill my oath to you.
God of the ancient light,
knowledge and wisdom,
grant me a loyal servant.
You're an Otome?
[ALL]
Huh?
[SLAVE B roars]
Huh? What's that?
A Slave!
[MASHIRO gasps]
It's looking at me!
[growls]
[ARIKA]
Look out!
[MASHIRO yelps]
[ALL scream]
[CROWD chatters]
[NINA grunts]
[MASHIRO, ARIKA gasp]
[growls]
Hurry up!
Think of something!
You're not my Master,
I can't do anything!
[NINA But if I defeat this
thing, Father will be proud.
I have an idea.
Please become my interim Master
and authorize the
use of my Robe.
Authorize? Do you mean...?
I do. Please hurry.
Very well. Your name is...?
[NINA]
Nina Wong.
All right, Nina Wong.
Otome of the Coral stone.
In my name, I hereby
release your powers!
Thank you, Master.
Materialize!
[shouts]
[computer beeps]
[YOHKO]
Huh?
[beeping continues]
It can't be!
[NATSUKI]
A Slave?
Are you sure
there's no mistake?
[YOHKO] Positive.
And from the same position,
I detected the Robe activation
of Coral Number One, Nina Wong.
I understand. Please keep
me posted, Professor Yohko.
Well, it seems that
Schwarz is here.
[NATSUKI]
In Wind City, yet.
Apparantly one of our
students is using her Robe.
That's a breach of our pact.
No, I don't think so.
Someone else in the area must
be giving her authorization.
Only one person in
Wind can do that.
[gasps]
The Princess!
[SHIZURU]
If that's really the case,
then the breach isn't
just on our side, is it?
Then it seems we have
an excuse to intervene.
OK, let's go.
It's time to
face the Schwarz.
Mind if I bring
one more person?
[shouts]
[NINA]
Even if I gather my power,
this Coral Robe isn't enough!
[ALL scream]
All right, now I'm mad!
Hey, wait! That's my--!
[ARIKA grunts]
Take this!
[roars]
Not good!
What were you thinking?
You've just gone and
made it even angrier!
[ARIKA gasps]
You're right!
[MASHIRO yelps]
[ARIKA]
Wait for me!
[ARIKA screams]
[NINA, MASHIRO gasp]
[SAKOMIZU] Have you ordered
the evacuation of the castle?
[SOLDIER 1B]
Yes, sir!
There's a fight after
50 years of peace.
[horn honking]
[SAKOMIZU]
Hm?
Akane, your job is to rescue
Nina and the Princess.
Yes, Headmistress.
Shizuru, you take
out the Slave.
Yes.
Just relax.
It'll be fine, Akane.
Right! Thank you,
Meister Shizuru!
Okay. Let them out!
I can't believe
this isn't a dream!
Is this the power of the Gem?
But...
Look! All the people down
there look like little peas!
[ALL]
Huh?
[ALL yelp]
[ALL scream]
[screams]
[NINA grunting]
[ARIKA screams]
[ARIKA gasps]
[NINA gasps]
[ARIKA screams]
[AKANE shouts]
[AKANE]
Are you three all right?
Thank you, Akane.
[ARIKA gasps]
[SAKOMIZU] We were
planning to engage it
on the way to the airport.
I never expected it to appear
right in the middle of the city.
[BOTH]
Huh?
[SAKOMIZU]
Wait...!
The Bewitching Smile Amethyst!
It's Meister Shizuru Viola!
[SOLDIER B]
The Otome's about to fight.
[SOLDIER C]
Are you sure?
[SHIZURU]
Now then.
It's time for a little
spring-cleaning.
[roars]
There seems to be something
on your head there.
[CROWD chatters]
Oh wow!
The appearance of a Slave.
The first Otome
battle in 50 years.
Looks like things
are getting hectic.
Huh? Neena- chan ?
Did you see that?
Should we follow?
[SAKOMIZU] Well, it was
fortunate we evacuated
everyone from the palace,
but what will the princess
say when she sees this?
[ARIKA gasps]
That was cool! Tell me,
what was that power?
That is the power
of the Otome.
And this is the school
that trains Otome;
Garderobe Academy.
Huh?
So this is Garderobe?
[NINA]
Father!
Nina- chan , I'm glad
you're all right.
Oh, and you're safe too!
[SERGEY]
The Blue Sky Sapphire?
[NINA]
Huh?
[ARIKA gasps, giggles]
[ARIKA cheers]
So cool!
I'm gonna be an Otome!
You can bet on that!
♪
[ARIKA] We were hot! And cute!
We're totally sizzlin'!
[NINA] Yes, we were.
But is that what we wanted?
[NATSUKI]
Don't worry about it.
[NINA]
Headmistress?
[NATSUKI] This is a sort
of tradition with us.
You'll soon understand.
[ARIKA] Then next time,
let's be super hot and cute!
[NINA, NATSUKI sigh]