For 15 years, I knew
the whole truth,
but up until now, I was too
frightened to say anything.
I convinced myself that
if that fake Princess
could govern the country well,
then that would be
an acceptable fate.
There would be no
need to disrupt things.
But now, my time in this
world is growing short,
and I felt I could no
longer hide the truth.
I had to tell someone...
The girl who holds
the Blue Sky Sapphire
is the true Queen of Windbloom.
What a terrible joke this is.
Now then, time to get
the party started!
Don't forget to take pictures.
We'll make a fortune.
I guess you could say
that we're having an early
Otome Graduation Ceremony.
[MEN laughing]
[ARIKA]
No!
[SERGEY]
Huh?
[ARIKA]
No... No!
Please stop!
[MAN A chuckles]
[MAN A]
You be a good little girl now.
[MEN chuckling]
[ARIKA]
Somebody... Sergey...
[SERGEY]
That's enough, you punks.
Huh?
Uh! Sergey...
[MAN A growls]
Arika?
You bastards!
Damn it! Get rid of him!
The next shots will hit you.
[MAN A]
Wait for me!
[MEN shouting]
[NAO]
Hi there.
We're Team Stripes and
we'll tear a strip off you.
So you guys were the ones
screwing around here, right?
Antsy, talk to me. Are you okay?
You must've been scared.
But it's all right now.
[crying]
Oh! Oh, please, Miss Juliet!
Can we give these guys
the 'ole water punishment?
Well, his isn't the first
crime for any of them.
Why don't we give them
double the usual?
[GANG MEMBER A]
Yes, ma'am!
Now that that's done,
let's see if the
victim will give us
a little financial reward
from the victim.
[ARIKA crying]
[gasps]
Ugh. What the hell is old
man Sergey doing here?
Arika?
Jeez.
Not only is she a fool,
she's got lousy luck.
[YAMADA] You're the man once
known as the "North Hound."
[ARIKA]
Sergey?
[SERGEY]
Huh?
Um... thank you.
Uh. Right.
You know, it sounds kinda weird.
This is the first time
I've heard anything
other than rude words
come outta your mouth.
Really? Am I always that bad?
I've only ever heard
you complain.
[whines]
You're teasing me!
[SERGEY chuckles]
That's more like
the Antsy I know.
[SERGEY] Here. It's getting
cold. You'd better wear this.
Why don't we go
for a little walk?
[MIMI]
Grandma!
Grandma, wake up! Grandma!
Grandma?
I... I can't stay here...
[knocking]
[SHIHO] Open up right
now, Miya! It's me!
Miya! Miya Clochette!
You've really done it
this time! The truth is out.
You're busted!
[gasps]
Why do these things keep
happening one after the other?
[TOMOE]
The Blue Sky Sapphire.
Huh. So that's why
Big Sister Shizuru...
[door opens]
[STUDENTS chattering]
[TOMOE]
Miya...
Huh. She was useless.
That piece of trash.
[CHIE]
Hmm.
I can't believe you, Miya.
I even allowed you to
take on room duty for me.
Guess I was mistaken about you.
Oh, really?
Are you sure this isn't because
you were maki-maki'ing
her behind her back?
Shut your big mouth!
Now that you've been
promoted to Trias,
purely by chance I might add,
you're just trying
to earn points!
You've got to be kidding me.
Becoming a member of Trias
is the last thing I wanted.
But hey, Chie, I was wondering,
what were you doing
in that place?
[CHIE]
I was on a date...
Well, actually, a friend of mine
who I met during exams
wanted to discuss
something with me.
Such the popular
girl, as always.
Hey, look who's talking.
So what did you do
with those guys?
Who knows?
Maybe you should go and check
the bottom of the river.
[ARIKA]
Ohh!
So pretty!
This is amazing!
It's so beautiful!
I thought you might enjoy
the view from up here.
To be in a place like this,
it just feels so wonderful...
All this technology
is like magic.
Well, from what I hear,
when our ancestory were
living on planet Earth,
they had even more
scientific advancements.
Even more?
I can't even imagine
such a thing.
But people in those times
must've been really happy
and lived great lives, right?!
You think so?
Well... I wonder.
[ARIKA]
Huh?
Uh, but there are some
things that I know.
That's the lighthouse
star, right?
Grandma told me that
it's from the time
of Grandma's Grandma's
Grandma, way, way back!
"The blue star shall
become the eternal sign,
to guide us and our beloved
Princess through the ages.
We shall journey past a thousand
stars and ten thousand nights,
toward the golden future
that will be upon us."
Do you know it?
It's a part of a long poem
that's said to have come
from the first people
that arrived here.
Have you heard it before?
[ARIKA]
Mh-hm.
But... it sounds wonderful.
The blue star that guides us...
The Blue Sky Sapphire...
You know about it?
[ARIKA]
Mh-hm.
The woman who held it was able
to accomplish her
dreams and find love.
[SERGEY]
Love, you say?
Arika... look, I...
Huh?
I just--
Sergey...
[ARIKA humming]
[ARIKA] Good morning! What a
wonderful day it is today!
Come on, Nina!
Time to wake up! Nina!
[NINA] Stop that...
What time d'you get back?
[ARIKA] I'm not gonna stop!
Get up, get up!
Arika!
[chuckles]
Thank goodness!
We were wondering when
you were gonna get back.
What are we waiting for?
The morning cleaning
is about to begin!
Let's be the first ones
out there! Let's go!
[NINA sighs]
Before you start
saying, "let's go,"
how about telling us
where you were last night?
[knocking]
[NINA]
Huh?
Come in.
Good morning!
Oh, I see you've finally made it
back from your night out, Arika.
Huh?
[ERSTIN]
Hm?
[NINA]
Huh?
Arika.
[ARIKA]
Huh?
Oh! Good morning to
you, Big Sister Chie!
[CHIE]
Hmm.
I have something to tell you.
Would you come with
me for a minute?
[ARIKA]
What?!
[CHIE]
She's confessed to everything.
That incident with your uniform
just after you entered
the Academy,
the problems you encountered
during the survival exam,
and now this latest incident.
Uh! What a total surprise!
So that's what was
really going on?!
But I thought her
uniform wasn't stolen.
[CHIE]
Apparently not.
You see, after
the survival test,
we found evidence
that your equipment
had been tampered with.
But at the time,
we had no evidence,
and we couldn't
make any accusations
until we had all the facts.
Please accept my
apologies for that.
Was Miya really the only girl
behind all of these events?
[CHIE]
Well, that's what she claims.
All of these incidents are
very sinister and cruel.
If you come forward as witnesses
to testify against her,
she can be dealt with properly
by the disciplinary committee.
So, what do you say?
I, uh, don't think I could.
How about you, Arika?
Huh?! What?! Who, me?!
Oh my gosh, no way!
I couldn't do such a thing!
I'm not really bothered
by it, honestly!
But wow. How could
Miya do such things?
I don't think anyone
would've guessed that!
What a total surprise!
What more can I say?
Arika?
[ARIKA laughing]
[NAO]
Huh?
Oh, come now.
Stop being so nice.
Don't you realize the chance
you've been given?
If you really are serious
about becoming an Otome,
you had better take
every opportunity
to get rid of your rivals.
You need all the
help you can get.
[ARIKA]
I said it's all right!
[BOTH gasp]
[NAO]
Uh?
What the...?
[door opens]
[MARIA]
What's all this noise about?
[ARIKA]
Huh?
Miss Maria. And Headmistress.
There is no longer any need
to discuss the issue
regarding Miya Clochette.
She has just withdrawn
herself from the Academy.
[ALL gasp]
We also received an official
notice from her guardian.
The letter mentions how
she had difficulty
in making it into
a higher ranking,
as well as the unstable
situation in her country.
Those are the reasons
why she's leaving.
Excuse me, I'd like
to see her off.
Would that be okay?
[MARIA]
Hm.
She has already left.
This whole thing leaves
a bad taste in my mouth.
[ERSTIN]
Mh-hm.
Look, Arika, I know that
this is gonna bother you,
but you shouldn't worry
too much about--
[bang]
[BOTH]
Huh?
[ERSTIN]
Arika, are you okay?
About what?
[NINA sighs]
Well, I'm glad to see
you're more immune
to these things than I expected.
Anyway, I have to get going.
I made a promise to
meet with my father.
Sergey...
[NINA]
Is something wrong?
[ARIKA]
Huh?
Oh, no. Nothing.
Go and have a great time!
[NINA]
Uh...
[ERSTIN] Hey, Arika?
Can I ask you something?
How did things go last night
with you and Major Wang?
Oh, sorry, I have to go now too!
To study... or, I mean, uh...
Anyway, I'm in a hurry!
Sorry, see you later!
Huh? Arika!
[sighs]
[AOI]
Arika?
Uh. Hello, Miss Aoi.
Hi there. Say, could
we talk for a minute?
[MIKOTO meows]
[knocking]
If it's a meeting, cancel it.
If it's a meal, I'm not hungry.
If it's a guest, send them away!
[door opens]
[ARIKA]
It's me, Mashiro!
Huh?
[ARIKA] I heard you locked
yourself up in this room.
What's wrong?
[MASHIRO]
It's none of your business!
Aw, you're being so mean.
I don't know if you remember,
but you and I still
have a contract.
[MASHIRO growls]
Shut up! You know that
contract was just for show!
I bet you thought...
I bet you thought the
same as everyone else.
That I'm not fit to be
this country's Queen!
[ARIKA]
So that's what happened.
[MASHIRO]
I'd been working so hard
and then that scoundrel
ruins everything.
I showed him a little kindness,
and how did he thank me?
By mocking me!
[ARIKA]
Huh?
Um... could it be that
you have feelings...
...for Prince Takumi no Kami?
Uh! What?
There's no way I could fall
in love with a guy like that!
It was just a temporary feeling.
But you just said it yourself.
[MASHIRO growls]
Listen, any more of that from
you and you're asking for it!
Besides, how would you know
anything about what goes on
between a guy and a
girl in the first place?
[chuckles nervously]
You know, you're right.
I don't know anything.
About love, or stuff like that.
Arika?
[ARIKA chuckles]
Huh?
Uh? What the--?
That's really strange.
What's wrong... with me?
Don't tell me that you...
have someone too?
Is it true?
[ARIKA]
Mh-hm.
Well, you are easy.
Huh?
You said yourself that
becoming an Otome
was the dream that
you finally found,
so I tested you to see
how difficult it would be
to distract you from it.
And you want to become a pure,
proper, and pretty Otome?
Huh! What a joke.
Not even close!
This is what always bothers me
about little girls like you.
You don't even put up a fight.
[SERGEY]
Playtime's over.
It's time you go home.
Oh, yeah. About Lena.
You were saying that she found
both her dreams and
her love, right?
Well you've got that part wrong.
She chose love and
gave birth to a child,
and therefore gave up
being an Otome.
Because of that, she was
unable to fight the rebels.
She failed to protect the King,
the Queen, and even herself,
and in the end, they all
died because of her.
I hate you!
Why? Why did I fall for him?
Y-You idiot!
Why are you crying?
I've been holding
it in for so long,
but if I see you cry like
this, I don't think I can...
[MASHIRO crying]
Mashiro... you too?
[MASHIRO]
Arika... you... stupid...
[ARIKA, MASHIRO crying]
[sighs]
Thank you, Chie.
It's just like you said.
[NINA]
He left on sudden notice? I see.
[NAGI]
"At last, we get the opportunity
to put our plan into action.
So I want you to find the true
Princess as soon as possible."
Your Highness...
[NAGI] If our dreams
are to be fulfilled,
it is crucial that we have the
real Princess in our hands.
[NAGI] I don't really
care how you do it,
but once you find her,
be sure to make her our pawn.
Why, you could always
just seduce her.
You're good at
that sort of thing.
But why... do I...?
It can't be.
She's the same age as Nina.
And besides, she's not even--
She's not even Lena's daughter.
But still...
[MASHIRO]
Here it is!
[ARIKA]
What's this?
It's a picture of what my
new castle will look like
when they're done building.
Looks kinda weird.
I think it's really inspiring.
Especially this big
sunflower on top!
[ARIKA]
Uhh...
Oh honestly, you have
no sense of beauty.
[ARIKA] Well, I do think
it suits you, Mashiro.
I wanna turn over a new leaf,
and be reborn like this castle.
Me too. Let's do our best then!
[MASHIRO]
Uh-huh.
Let's make it a race.
We'll see if I become
a Meister first,
or you become a Queen first!
How about it?
I already am a Queen!
Uhh...
Then how about... a Queen
who will bring happiness
to everyone in her country?
[MASHIRO]
Uh...
Good idea!
Okay! The race is on!
[BOTH chuckle]
[MARIA] We will now begin
the first round of battles
to determine the representatives
for the commemorative
graduation dance-battle.
There will be two
representatives.
Those who are chosen will be
unconditionally promoted
to Pearl status.
Give it your best.
[MASHIRO]
Arika!
Don't you dare lose, okay?
[TOMOE] It's a parting gift.
Please accept it.
We are all going to miss you.
But just so you know...
...I will never forget
about you, dear Miya.
Now, begin!
[MASHIRO] Arika, who was
your special someone?
[ARIKA]
Don't tell anyone...
[MASHIRO] An older man who
serves royalty and knows me?
I know! Wow, you sure
have bad taste!
[ARIKA gasps]
[MASHIRO]
Sakomizu?!
[ARIKA]
What?! It's not him!