My... birthday?
Yeah.
I realized the other day
that I'd forgotten to
ask you about it.
I certainly hope it
hasn't passed yet.
So when is it, Nina? Is it soon?
[NINA]
Uh... Mh-hm..
[SERGEY]
Huh?
Mm. I see. I'm sorry.
Hmm...
Well... how 'bout we
make it September 7th?
I'm off work that day, so we
can have a big birthday party!
[gasps]
So think about what you
want for your present!
Are you all right, Sergey?
[NINA]
Father...
Sergey...
[NAGI]
I'm sure one thing is clear.
You'd better not think
of betraying me.
Yes.
Anyway, you still have
a job to focus on.
It's up to you to find
the real Princess.
[SERGEY]
Right.
Because whoever controls her
can control the entire world.
[knocking]
Another tax hike?
Yes.
The Queen's forcing it through.
She wants it to
bypass the committee.
The costs of the coronation
and castle repairs
have really depleted
the national treasury.
On top of that, the Queen's
birthday is approaching,
and the entire kingdom
will be celebrating that.
This increase is probably
to cover those costs.
[SERGEY] The unemployment
rates are skyrocketing,
but they're all so carefree.
Let's see... what day is
Queen Mashiro's birthday again?
Huh?
Well then, I'd better make
sure I don't forget.
The real Princess...
[IRINA]
Really? That's a great!
[LILIE] Yeah, Arika,
you're ranked 29th now?
That's a huge improvement!
But I couldn't have done so well
without Ersty and Irina's help!
Don't talk with your
mouth full, Arika!
Thank you so much!
Man, I can't believe it.
It's a wonder that you
rose to 29th place.
Well, she did challenge the
survival test by herself.
And she broke the record
for the fastest time.
[LILIE chuckles]
[IRINA]
Huh?
[YAYOI]
C'mon, cheer up, Erstin!
Even though you couldn't
retake that test,
you still came in 30th!
I think that's pretty good!
Let's do our best next time!
I'll do anything I can
to help you out, Ersty!
And all of us will reach
for our dreams together!
[ALL chuckle nervously]
Aw, thank you, Arika.
And Nina and Tomoe both held on
to their first and
second places.
Well, it's not like
I did anything special.
Ahh...
Just once I wanna say that too.
Stand at the top, and say,
"I didn't do anything special."
[ARIKA, ERSTIN, YAYOI,
LILIE laughing]
[YAYOI]
It's not like you.
[IRINA]
No?
[NATSUKI] So, we're the ones
who hide technology away
and cause disorder in the world.
Huh.
Those are rather
painful words to hear.
That power of theirs...
Tey've analyzed
body-implant nanomachines
and learned how to control them.
[SHIZURU]
They don't appear to have
the power or technology
to materialize a Robe yet.
But that's only
a matter of time.
If they keep blindly
grasping at power like that,
it will only lead
to destruction!
Why won't they understand that?
[SHIZURU] I'm also worried
about what's contained
in that data pod.
I wonder who the Aswad
are working for.
It could be Cardair,
or maybe Florince?
Ever since that organ
note was heard,
it seems that everyone has
been acting suspiciously.
Peace is very weak...
and fragile.
It can be easily broken,
even though it was
bought with the sacrifices
of so many Otomes.
Don't forget,
no matter what happens,
I'll always be by
your side, Natsuki.
Oh, Nina.
Uh... Tomorrow is
your birthday, right?
Would you mind if I gave
you a present, then?
[YAYOI]
What? Are you serious?
Tomorrow's Nina's birthday?
That's cool.
Did you know that you have
the exact same birthday
as Queen Mashiro?
What?! Mashiro's birthday
is tomorrow too?!
Yeah! That means we're
gonna have a big party!
No. There's no need for that.
Aww!
All you hafta do is smile
and say "great idea!"
Really, Nina, you're not being
honest with your feelings.
[NINA screams]
[NINA growls]
Arika!
[MARIA]
Girls.
[BOTH gasp]
Just because you've
completed your exams
doesn't mean you can
stand around wasting time.
Nina Wang, Arika Yumemiya,
please come with me.
I have something to discuss
with the both of you.
[BOTH]
Huh?
[ARIKA groans]
[ARIKA] They called us in to
give us extra work to do!
Extra work?
[ARIKA]
Mh-hm.
Something about some
Prince from another country
coming to visit the
academy tomorrow.
[NINA]
He's from Zipang.
It's the country on the far
eastern coast of the continent.
So we have to serve as
attendants to Mashiro
when she welcomes him.
[ERSTIN gasps]
But that's wonderful!
What's that, by the way?
Oh! It's something from
the man sponsoring me.
I don't know what it is though!
What about yours, Nina?
Oh, this? Well...
[gasps]
Wow...
I know...
But what is it? It's not
a necklace, is it?
[NINA]
Huh?
[SERGEY]
"My dearest Nina.
Congratulations on
your 15th birthday.
You're always in my
thoughts. Sergey."
[ARIKA gasps]
[ERSTIN gasps]
This looks wonderful, too!
[ARIKA gasping]
Do you think all these clothes
will look good on me?
Yeah! I do!
[IRINA]
Wow!
There's everything a girl
would ever want in there!
Yeah, but why would he
give me this stuff?
Huh?
"You seem to have worked
hard on your exam.
This birthday present is
also to congratulate you
on your great effort.
I hope you become a great Otome.
Happy 15th birthday,
and do your best."
Huh? Hey, what's
the date tomorrow?
Uh, it's September 7th.
That's right!
Tomorrow's my birthday!
[NINA]
Huh?
He is so amazing!
Even I had forgotten about it!
So wait a minute!
That means that you and
Nina have your birthdays
on the same day.
[ERSTIN]
And so does Queen Mashiro.
[IRINA]
What a coincidence!
It really is! Right, Nina?
Nina...
Well... how 'bout we
make it September 7th?
That person...
She was my dream once.
[SERGEY]
The Blue Sky Sapphire?!
Is that the reason?
Is it, Father?
[growls]
[BOTH chuckle nervously]
Why?! Today is my
birthday, after all.
So why should I waste it
welcoming some Prince
from a foreign country?
Well, for one thing,
I hear he's a very handsome
Prince, Miss Mashiro!
And there are other reasons
too! Right, minister?
[SAKOMIZU gasps]
Uh... that's right!
In order to properly welcome
a nation's Prince,
we really must have you present.
I don't suppose you two are
hiding anything from me?
We'd do such a thing, right?
Uh.
Right. We're not hiding a thing.
[AOI] Thank goodness she
didn't find anything out.
Yes.
If she knew we were trying
to arrange a marriage--
[AOI]
Don't talk about that here!
[meows]
Hey, Nina, wait up!
What are you so
angry about anyway?
I'm not angry.
Hey!
[ARIKA]
This station!
Standing here reminds me
of the first time we met.
And back then, you had the
same mad look on your face
that you have now.
I did not.
[ARIKA]
Mh-hm! Yes, you did!
No, I didn't!
[ARIKA] Huh? What's the
matter with that kid?
Do you think he's lost?
[gasps]
Hey! Hey, kid!
Hm?
[NINA]
What's wrong?
Are you alone?
Where are your
mother and father?
Give me a minute, okay?
Huh?
Mh-hm. Of course!
[NINA]
Come on. Let's go.
[ARIKA chuckles]
What is it? You can't
seem to stop smiling.
I'm just feeling kinda happy
because I finally got to see
how nice you can be.
Shut up. It was nothing special,
just common sense.
Right, nothing special!
Anyway, it's taking a long
time for the monorail--
What's wrong?
My watch!
[STATION EMPLOYEE A]
Huh? Hey, wait! Kid!
Stop!
Is that you're...?
Nina!
Nina! I'll help you out!
No! You need to go and
welcome the Prince!
Hey, I've always been
really good at playing tag!
[ARIKA]
Huh? I know this place.
I'm taking a shortcut!
Huh?
Okay, stop right there!
[MIMI yelps]
[NINA]
Give that back to me!
It's important to me!
I'm begging you!
[stomach growls]
If you're hungry,
I can give you money,
or anything you'd like!
Huh?
[growls]
[gasps]
Nina!
Hey, you!
Wait, please stop! Come back!
[ARIKA]
Huh?
What?!
No, Nina, you can't!
[NINA screams]
Otomes can't take their
clothes off in public!
Let me go!
That pocket watch!
It's my father's pocket watch!
Even with your strength, Nina,
you can't catch up
to it by swimming!
But it's my...
[MAN A]
Aww, is it over already?
[MAN B]
Aren't ya gonna strip anymore?
Shut up, you jerks!
Stop looking!
[MEN laughing]
Mikoto! C'mon!
[MIKOTO meows]
[BOTH yelp]
Stop the car, now!
[AOI]
Miss Mashiro!
Yeah, I seen that watch.
Where is it? I'll give you
anything in return for it!
So please.
The thing is,
right after I found it,
this darn crow
came outta nowhere!
And it snatched the thing away.
So where can we find this crow?
[MAN C] Aw, jeez.
How the heck should I know?
I bet the crow comes
from this forest.
I'll ask around to see
if anyone's seen it.
Don't... bother.
Huh? What?
I said don't bother searching!
But... it's very
important to you, right?
And it has that chain you got as
a birthday present from Sergey!
I don't care...
about my birthday!
How 'bout we make it
September 7th?
[SERGEY]
The Blue Sky Sapphire?!
[SERGEY] That person...
She was my dream once.
He chose this day as my
birthday... only because...
...it's your... it's that
woman's daughter's birthday...
So you...
Nina?
It's all a lie anyway!
[SERGEY] Are you sure
that this is all you want?
Uh-huh.
[SERGEY] But this is just
a cheap little thing
I bought with my first paycheck.
I can get you something better.
[NINA]
Mh-hm.
I want the one you have, Father.
Well then, it's yours now,
Nina. Happy Birthday.
I need to know why...
Why are you here, Arika?
Why did you have
to come here now?
You show up in
front of my father
wearing that damn gemstone.
Why?
If you hadn't shown up, Father
would be watching only me.
No one else, just me! Forever!
Even if he only sees
me as a daughter...
...I still want him to...
Who wants to have an
arranged marriage?
Ahh! It's been a long time.
Now to go incognito
and see how my citizens are
celebrating my birthday!
Let's go!
Huh?
[yowling]
[screeching]
[MIKOTO, CROW A screeching]
[yowls]
[screches]
[growling]
Mikoto!
[BOY]
Uh... are you all right?
Uhh...
Um, you mean you have
feelings for Sergey?
[ARIKA gasps]
I mean... Major Wang, of course.
Do you... like him?
[NINA gasps]
And what about you?
[ARIKA]
Huh?
What happened then?
In the survival test,
when you two were alone?
[gasps]
Nothing happened! Nothing!
It's true that he saved me,
but that's it! Nothing more!
[grumbles]
[ARIKA gasps]
[ARIKA]
Huh?
Then this is all the more reason
why we have to find
that pocket watch!
Huh?
Grandma told me that
if you get something
from a person important to you,
then that thing
is important too!
Arika...
[SERGEY]
Well, hello there, girls.
What're you two doing out here?
Are you lost?
Last I heard, you girls
are supposed to go
and pick up the
Prince of Zipang.
[NINA]
Father.
Sergey.
[NINA]
Listen up. Act normally.
If you tell him what I said,
you're dead meat.
Oh, we're on our way right now.
We still had some time,
so we took a detour.
And came all the way out here?
Never mind.
I'm glad I found you.
[ARIKA gasps]
We've been looking
all over for that!
[NINA growls]
[ARIKA whimpers]
Just as I thought, you've
been out here looking for it.
Honestly, ditching
academy work for this?
I'm very sorry, Father, but I...
It's okay.
I'm glad to see you like
the chain for your watch.
[sighs]
Well then, one more time.
Have a happy birthday, Nina.
My goodness, you
certainly have grown!
It's hard to believe
that it's been exactly
six years since we met.
Exactly?
[SERGEY]
Hm?
Wait a minute, are you telling
me you don't already know that?
Well, come to think of it,
I guess that's natural
because you were in the hospital
for a while after we met.
[NINA]
Huh?
That's how I chose your
birthday. It's September 7th.
Because that's the day
you and I first met.
Thank you, Father.
What's gotten into you?
Nina- chan .
[ARIKA]
I'm happy for you, Nina.
[thumping]
[ARIKA]
Huh?
So... what're we gonna do?
I don't know why
you're asking me.
I have no idea
what we should do.
His Grace has arrived!
The Prince of Zipang!
Thank you everyone! I am honored
by this warm reception!
[ARIKA] Wow... so big
and white and soft.
[ERSTIN] Stop staring at it.
I'm embarrassed.
[ARIKA]
Hey, do you mind if I lick it?
[IRINA]
Wh-Wh-What are you two doing?!
[ERSTIN]
I'm making a cake.
[ARIKA]
It's my birthday present!
[IRINIA gasps]