So in the end, the
Harmonium had been moved
into the basement
of Fuka Castle.
It's hard to believe.
For centuries people
have searched for it,
but no one was able to
determine where it was.
And now that girl happens
to find it so easily...
She just might be...
[SHIZURU]
I wonder what really happened.
Do you think the two of them
have made a contract?
[NATSUKI]
Probably.
They seem to think they're doing
a sufficient job of
hiding it from us.
[SHIZURU] Should we make
them cancel the contract?
I'd rather let events
unfold on their own.
It's a long shot,
but it is possible
that this could be a
critical turning point.
You're just gonna
leave it to chance?
This may turn out to be
what fate's decided.
If that's the way
you feel, Natsuki,
I won't argue with you.
In the meantime, I'll see
if I can persuade her
to tell me what happened
below the castle.
Thank you.
Anyway, now that the Harmonium's
been heard once again,
we've bigger problems
to deal with.
I have a feeling that
even as we speak
people everywhere are being
informed of the news.
Now, everything has
been set in motion.
[ARIKA panting]
[ARIKA groans]
This punishment
duty is too harsh!
Just because I skipped some of
the dance-battle lessons...
Well, I can't help that!
It's not my fault I can't
take this thing off.
[sighs]
[IRINA] Who told you that
you could take a break?!
[yelps]
[IRINA]
Arika Yumemiya!
[ARIKA]
I'm very sorry! I was just...
Huh?
[ARIKA]
Oh! Yummy!
Delicious! Thank you
so much, Ersty!
My stomach was really growling!
it must be tough
cleaning so big a place.
[IRINA] Well, guess
that can't be helped.
This is the burial ground for
the first Meister Otome, Fumi.
Hey, I've heard about her!
She had something
to do with some war?
The War of the Twelve Kings?
Right! And she's the
one who ended the war.
Mashiro told me!
[ERSTIN chuckles]
You and Queen
Mashiro really seem
to be getting along well, Arika!
[ARIKA]
No, it's not like that.
[NINA] A contract?!
Between Arika and Queen Mashiro?
[SERGEY]
It appears that way.
Probably with the
Blue Sky Sapphire.
[gasps]
You mean she was accepted
by the Meister Gem
and was able to use its power?
I'm so sorry, Nina- chan .
I hate to ask you to do these
kinds of things for me.
I understand, Father.
I'll try and get the
whole story out of her.
[ERSTIN] By the way,
how's your ear, Arika?
[ARIKA yelps]
I-It's all right. Uh, it's
just a little infection.
Arika.
Yeah, Nina?
It's nothing. Never mind.
Uh... well, okay then...
I'd better get back to work!
Thanks for lunch!
[IRINA]
Stop right there!
I've got a little
present to give you!
[ARIKA]
Oh, did you get me dessert?
Uh-uh-uh. I've got
something even better.
[ARIKA]
Huh?
[ARIKA] Ah! Wow!
Look at that! A machine!
Irina, you built this yourself?
Oh, this is nothing in
the scheme of things.
I mean, our ancestors
used the power of science
to travel through space
and come to this planet.
Does it move?
Of course it does!
I got some parts from junk
shops and antique stores,
and I swiped... I mean, borrowed
the rest from Miss Yohko.
Behold the power of
Mister Cleaner One!
[groans]
That's amazing! It moved!
And now there's
smoke coming out!
What does it do next?
Tell me, tell me!
I guess the data
was insufficient.
[IRINA] Oh man, I wish
I could sneak a peek
at what's on the other
side of that door.
I was hoping to
present this machine
for the research portion
of our next interim exam.
There's an exam?
That's right. They start soon.
What? Really?
ctually, Arika, I haven't
seen you study much.
Are you gonna be okay?
If you come last in two
consecutive terms,
you'll be expelled.
[ARIKA gasps]
I'll be fine... No problem...
[ARIKA]
Ugh!
Nothing.
I've been through every
one of these books,
and I still can't find anything
about how to cancel a contract.
[SHIZURU]
Are you doin' some research?
[ARIKA]
Miss Shizuru!
Well, um, that is, I'm...
studying for the final exams!
Well that's good to hear.
If you'd like, I can help
you with your studies.
Huh?
She's so lucky!
I can't believe she's
getting private tutoring
from Miss Shizuru!
I'm so jealous!
But really, it's not fair.
Arika always gets
all the attention.
[ARIKA]
Huh?
Did you hear that
noise the other day?
There was a terrific
sound like thunder
and it shook the entire city.
Well, I didn't notice anything.
And I didn't hear any
organ playing, either.
Is that so?
[ARIKA sighs]
That was a close call.
I almost slipped up and told
Miss Shizuru what happened.
But she's been so nice
to me... She's wonderful.
I wish I knew if my mother
was also wonderful like that.
Okay! I gotta give it my best!
[gasps]
[IRINA] Thank you!
I learned a lot from this.
But I guess it didn't help
that much in the end, did it?
I'm sorry.
Don't apologize. That's your
dad's most valuable book.
I'm just honored to
have the opportunity
to read such a rare book
about artificial intelligence.
Hey, where's Arika?
She's not back yet.
[NINA]
Hm?
[ARIKA]
Ah, there it is!
Jeez, don't scare me like that!
You always like to appear out
of thin air, don't you, Miyu?
Forgive me, Arika.
[ARIKA]
It's been a long time!
How'd you find out that I've
been going to Garderobe Academy?
Because I know everything
about you, Arika.
And good evening
to you, Alyssa!
[MIYU] I see. So your
grandmother has...?
Yeah.
She died about six months
after your last visit.
Have you been enjoying
yourself at school?
Yeah!
It's kinda tough,
because there's a lot
of studying and work,
but becoming a great
Otome is my dream!
It's really hard though...
Oh, hey, Miyu,
you've been traveling
for a long time, right?
Yes.
Then I have to
ask you something.
Have you ever heard of a
way to cancel a contract
made with a Meister Gem?
This thing is, well...
[chirps]
Who goes there?
[MASHIRO yelping]
Hey, how rude!
Mashiro?
Arika! What are you doing?
Are you outta your mind?
You know who this girl is?
[ARIKA] Huh? Oh, yes!
This is Mashiro.
She's the Queen of Windbloom,
believe it or not!
What do you mean,
"believe it or not"?
Look, I thought we had
agreed that the incident
regarding the Gems
was our little secret!
But here you are,
blathering about it to some
suspicious vagabond!
Don't worry, the
secret's safe with Miyu.
She's not from the
school, and besides,
she knows all kinds
of interesting things!
Be quiet! Remember your place.
Huh?
I will not allow you
to insult Arika further.
[MASHIRO]
How dare you be disrespectful!
By the way, Mashiro,
what are you doing here?
I'm here because you
haven't come and told me
how to cancel
this contract!
Do you know how hard it is to
sneak out here to see you?
Hey!
Look, I'm doing my best
to figure out a way.
Is that Gem the
cause of the problem?
Yeah.
Is it all right if I
take a look at it?
[ARIKA]
Go ahead.
A real Meister Gem. This
is truly a great Gemstone.
[ARIKA]
Yeah, isn't it?
You should see what it can do!
Uh?
She took it off?!
H-How did you do that?!
I tried everything I
could to get it off.
Th-Then how about this one?
Can you take mine off too?
Give it a try, Miyu!
Of course, Arika.
Oh my gosh!
[ARIKA]
It came off!
[MASHIRO gasps]
That's great. That means...
...our contract is cancelled.
[MIYU]
I'm afraid that's not so.
I've heard that even if the
Gemstones are removed,
the contract etched
into them remains.
Aww...
Then, how do we
break the contract?
Come on! Help us out!
[MIYU]
I do not know.
Perhaps you should formally
ask the academy for assistance.
If I could, I would.
We're trying to keep
this whole thing a secret.
In that case...
[IRINA] Sneak into
the forbidden library?!
Why are you in such a rush
to break the rules again?
That library has the
records of all Otomes
and information on the
school's history, right?
Well, I heard that it's like
a mountain of treasure in there,
with countless books on
this planet's history
and the lost
technology of Earth.
But if we get caught,
it's over. We're done for!
I don't care. I hafta
learn about the Otomes.
Arika, you said your mother was
also an Otome, isn't that right?
[ARIKA]
Uh-huh.
All right then,
I'm going to join you.
[IRINA] I wasn't
expecting that from you.
[ARIKA]
Thank you, Nina!
Don't get the wrong idea.
I'm not doing this for you.
I want to know myself.
If that's the case, I'll
just have to go along too!
You can count me in!
I guess I'll go too.
[ARIKA]
Mh-hm!
We'll all go!
Yeah, but how are we
supposed to get in there?
It's really difficult
to break into.
I have an idea how to get in.
It's kinda creepy in here.
[ARIKA] This place is the grave
of the very first Otome, right?
[ERSTIN]
I heard she rests in peace
somewhere deep underground.
Hey, Arika.
Will you take that
ridiculous thing off?
[ARIKA] But Grandma always said
that this is proper attire
for sneaking into places
you're not supposed to go.
Take it off.
[ARIKA whines]
So everyone's here now?
[NAGI]
Hey.
Would you be the one that
sent me that love letter?
I have to confess that
I was very surprised.
Huh, I thought it would
be a letter telling me
to use Slaves and fight.
In a way, that is very close to
what its actual contents are.
It is a pleasure to finally
meet you, Grand Duke Nagi.
[IRINA] But how were you
able to get your hands
on the key to the
forbidden library?
That's a trade secret.
Don't forget our deal.
You guys are going to
help me out with my work
once this is done.
If it's only work,
just leave it to me!
That includes you, Nina.
Y-Yes.
Well then, let's go.
[IRINA]
Is it open now?
The lock is open, but there
should be another step
to actually getting
the door open.
At least, there was
the last time I tried.
Then how about... a password?
Like "open sardine"!
[ARIKA chuckles]
Sardine?
[ALL gasp]
The door...
It really opened...
...with... "sardine"?
I will not tolerate
failure, Arika.
This is the library?
[ERSTIN] There certainly
are a lot of books.
This place is amazing.
[IRINA] What did you
do this time, Arika?
[ARIKA]
Don't ask me!
What is this?
This is absolutely incredible!
I'll bet this thing
is the databank.
It has information from
before the Immigration,
back when people would
travel in spaceships.
[ARIKA]
Databank?
[ERSTIN]
I've heard of them before.
They're supposed to be
like one giant library.
S-So what do we do with it?
To access something like this,
we would need some
sort of password,
or maybe another item
that can act as a key.
Wait, a key?
You're expecting too much of me.
[ARIKA sighs]
How come it disappeared?
[ERSTIN] Huh? There seems to be
something else back there.
What is this place?
Whatever they are, they all
have some kind of inscription.
Let's see...
The Flowing Garnet,
Meister Monica Julen,
devoted her life to Master Argos
the Twelfth of Cardair.
Year A.R. 264 to 281.
[ERSTIN, IRINA gasp]
Year 281... that was...
That was 50 years ago,
at the end of the
last major war,
the War of the Dragon King.
You mean, these things are...?
[MARIA]
They're tombstones.
This is the resting place of
your Otome predecessors.
[gasps]
This time, you girls have
truly stepped over the line.
These are sacred grounds.
No one is not allowed to
enter without permission.
No students,
not even royalty itself.
And all of these... are graves?
I deeply apologize for the
disgrace, Big Sister Monica.
[IRINA]
Um... was she someone you knew?
Yes.
When we were in school,
I was assigned to be her
helper underclassman,
and I performed
room duty for her.
She was extraordinary.
She served as a
member of the Trias.
She was elegant and pure.
But that was in a time when
the world was nowhere near
as peaceful and
stable as it is today.
Every country wanted power,
and there were many
international wars.
This finally culminated in
the War of the Dragon King.
[MARI] In the midst of
the never-ending battles,
the Otomes would find
themselves chosen as Meisters
and sent to the battlefield,
one by one,
even before their graduation.
Then through the contracts
with their masters,
they performed their
responsibilities and duties.
[ARIKA]
Duties?
[NINA] They fought, didn't they?
The Otome fought each other.
[gasps]
[MARIA]
That's correct.
And the person who defeated
Big Sister Monica
was the Number Two Pearl,
the second member of Trias,
and her dearest friend
at the academy.
Why'd that hafta happen?
They should've just refused
to fight each other!
Stop saying such
foolish nonsense, girl.
That was not even possible.
The fate of the war and
the lives of the rulers
rested in the hands
of the Otomes.
That's how the countries and all
of the citizens could survive.
Most importantly, as Otomes,
the girls had complete
trust, respect, and love
for their Masters.
These bonds were stronger
and more honorable
than their bonds of friendship,
and they acted accordingly.
Listen to me carefully.
Today, people see and honor
only the elegant side of Otomes,
as women who serve royalty.
But if things ever go wrong,
even best friends will
be forced to strike down
and kill each other.
That is the destiny of an Otome.
Are all of you truly
prepared to do that?
Yes, I'm prepared to do it.
No! I won't!
Then leave this school
immediately, Arika Yumemiya.
All we need to do is make
sure wars don't happen!
When I become a proper Otome,
I won't allow any wars!
How wonderful it would
be if that were possible.
Now, we've been here
too long already.
We shall apologize
to your Big Sisters
for disturbing their sleep,
and then make our way out.
Arika. That's disrespectful
to your Big Sisters.
Take that off!
Uh! No!
[gasps]
Arika!
It's gone!
A-A-Arika Yumemiya...
Ah... um... well... you see...
[chuckles nervously]
[IRINA]
I heard it's been four years
since anyone's had to clean
these walls as punishment.
But at least there's
a bright side, Arika.
You were able to get a new
Coral Gem in the end.
That's true.
But I still haven't been able
to cancel the contract yet.
[NAO]
Hey, guys?
Don't forget that you still need
to help me with my job too.
[ALL]
Right.
Hey, Arika!
[yelps]
You told them about
the Gemstones breaking!
Thanks to you, I got
in big trouble too!
I had no choice!
Besides, we had to do something
about the broken stones anyway.
You are really not
cut out to be an Otome!
Hurry up and get
expelled already! Ugh!
Ha! You wish!
If someone like her
were my Master,
my friends would be a lot
more important to me.
For sure.
And the fact is,
the world is a whole lot
better than it used to be.
It's not like a war's
gonna break out!
Huh?
Yeah. Right!
[NINA]
Hmm...
[RAD] I see. It's within
the borders of Aries.
And you want us to retrieve it.
[ARGOS]
Indeed. The time is ripe.
We have to start
moving right away.
[RAD]
What we find, we split evenly.
Those are the terms.
Ha. It appears you're as
greedy as the rumors say.
Very well,
I accept your terms.
[RAD]
Commander.
[MIDORI]
In that case,
we of the Aswad shall
take on your request,
Emperor Argos of Cardair.
You better watch what you say!
It's all right, Fia.
These people are reactionaries,
waiting for the chance to revert
back to the interplanetary era.
Am I right, Leader of Aswad?
Yes, you are.
We are the last descendants
of the Black Valley.
[ERSTIN] So, Nina, what
exactly are we doing
to help Big Sister Nao?
[NINA]
Well... about that...
[NAO] It's nothing, just a
little... physical service.
[ERSTIN]
Physical? That isn't right!
Oh, but if it was...
[NAO]
You know, I am constantly amazed
at your choice of friends.
[NINA chuckles]