[NAGI] So this girl
wants to be an Otome.
Isn't that right?
What's the problem?
Let her join.
What?
Then how's this for a solution?
As entertainment for dear
Mashiro's coronation ceremony,
why not have Nina and this girl
engage in a dance-battle?
The winner stays at the academy.
The loser leaves!
Not a bad idea, huh?
[NINA] I will participate
in this challenge.
I beg the council...
Allow me the chance
to fight against this girl!
[COUNCIL REPS chattering]
[SERGEY]
Huh?
A fight?
What do you think, Mashiro?
Nina thinks it's
a wonderful idea.
Why should I listen
to any of your ideas?
Y'know, I take it all back.
[COUNCIL REPS gasp]
[NAGI]
Now that I think about it,
I realize what a headache it
would be for me if Nina lost.
After all, she's the girl who
might become my future Otome.
Sorry about that.
Let's forget it.
You're kidding!
--[MASHIRO] Okay!
--[NINA] Huh?
You two should
go through with it.
I wish to see your dance power
at my coronation ceremony!
[ARIKA]
Huh?
[NAGI]
What? No way!
[CHILDREN laughing]
[RAD]
They're coming.
Hey!
Make sure this thing's secured!
We can't afford to have
this fall on the guests,
so be careful!
And that's the outline
of our security measures.
Any questions?
My castle is still
in that awful state.
Look here, this isn't a farce
for Nagi and the other
leaders to laugh at.
You'd better get it right!
[SAKOMIZU]
Uh, right.
And one more thing,
about that dance battle...
Due to the tight
schedule and budget
in regards to the facilities,
the Minister of Internal
Affairs would like you
to consider
canceling the battle.
How dare you suggest
I back out and lose face?!
The princess loses her cool
when it comes to
Grand Duke Nagi.
That's why she always
plays right into his hands.
[MASHIRO growling]
[YOHKO]
Are you all right?
Please let me know if you
feel any pain or discomfort.
[ARIKA]
I feel fine!
Absolutely no problem!
I see.
You really are compatible
with the nanomachines.
That's rare.
The average girl
has complications
and can even be
bedridden for days.
Compatible?
Um... you mean... with those...
What are they called again?
Nanomachines?
That's right.
We insert tiny machines
that allow you to materialize
the Elements for a
Robe from your body,
as well as strengthen
your muscles
and improve your
ability to heal.
Garderobe Academy is the
only place on the planet
that still has this technology.
[ARIKA]
Wow, that's awesome!
It's like a mystery of science!
Now I'll be able to wear one
of those cool-looking dresses!
[laughing]
But without a GEM,
you can only wear them once.
[ARIKA]
What?
Have you noticed
that all the students
have a single pierced ear?
Those are called GEMs,
and they control an
Otome's nanomachines.
[ARIKA] Then please
give me an earring too!
Only after you become
a student of the Academy.
[ARIKA]
Oh, man!
That means I won't get one
until after I defeat Nina!
[NATSUKI]
I don't believe this.
All because that
idiotic princess
played right into
Grand Duke Nagi's hands!
Things have gotten
much more complicated.
[SHIZURU] Natsuki, your
forehead's getting all wrinkled!
[NATSUKI]
Ugh...
Well, seems to me
the best thing to do
is just go with
the flow for now.
Yeah.
All the same,
Nina's not an opponent
who can be pushed
around easily.
We should be thinking
about our next step.
You're right.
I don't know if you've heard,
but the students are already
making a big fuss about this.
[LILIE]
What? Are you positive?
[MIYA]
Yeah!
Nina is betting her
enrollment in this academy
on a dance-battle against
that weird naked girl!
[YAYOI] And it's happening at
Princess Mashiro's coronation!
[STUDENT 3A] If that girl wins,
she gets to enroll.
[STUDENT 3B]
What? That is so unfair!
[SHIHO] This whole thing
is just crazy!
[CHIE] Really? I find
it all very interesting.
[IRINA] Well, knowing Nina,
she'll win this easily.
[ERSTIN]
Yeah, I guess so.
[IRINA laughs] You worry
way too much, Erstin!
[ERSTIN] Well, ever since
they decided to have
the dance-battle,
Nina's been acting really quiet.
--[SERGEY] Nina!
--[NINA] Huh?
[NINA]
Father...
How are you doing, my dear?
Everything is fine.
I will do my best.
I will not bring public dishonor
to you or the Grand Duke.
You are worrying
too much about it.
Just fight with your usual
skill, and there's no chance
that you'll lose.
But that... strange girl...
[NINA]
Huh?
[giggles]
Oh!
[SERGEY]
What's wrong?
I am... allowed to win, right?
Now isn't that obvious?
I would be ruined if you didn't.
[NINA]
I understand.
I'll do my best.
[SERGEY] That sounds more
like my daughter, Nina- chan .
[SERGEY]
Just great.
The Grand Duke gets
another one of his ideas
and I get a ton of work. Hm?
♪ [ARIKA] ...tell
of an old story ♪
♪ Of a land that waits to wake ♪
[SERGEY]
It can't be...
♪ [ARIKA]
...the light that shines ♪
♪ Lives in hearts
that never quake ♪
♪ I can see what
tomorrow brings ♪
♪ And my wish to become a star ♪
♪ To my loved one
I must say... ♪
♪ Wa-- ♪
Huh?
Hey, Antsy, that song...
Stop calling me "Antsy!"
Look, it can't be helped
if you look like one.
[ARIKA]
Will you shut up?!
What are you doing
out here anyway?!
I was about to
ask you the same.
I was told...
Let's see...
I have to rest quietly until
my body gets used to those...
...uh, nanomachine thingamajigs.
Are you seriously
thinking of fighting Nina?
[ARIKA]
Of course I am!
[SERGEY]
You're being foolish.
Nina's very strong.
And since it's your
first time with a Robe,
you have no chance of winning.
I already made up my mind!
I'll become an Otome!
Being an Otome's my dream!
Hmph. Dream, huh?
Tell me, do you really
know what's involved?
Do you have any idea what it
takes to become an Otome?
Besides, even if
you somehow win,
you'll be crushing
the dreams of Nina,
who has endured strenuous
training to enter the academy.
Is your dream really
worth that much to you?
Grandma always told me,
"It's important to have a
dream, no matter what.
And once you have a dream,
never give it up."
Back then, I didn't
understand what she meant.
But you know?
I came here and saw the Meister
Otome's battle, and I knew!
"This is it! Yeah!"
I finally found my dream.
So I'll keep chasing
after it, no matter what.
[SERGEY]
I understand.
I won't say another word.
Keep chasing after your dream.
Well, duh!
[SERGEY chuckles]
[SERGEY]
By the way.
That song...
[ARIKA] Oh, my grandmother
sang it to me all the time.
She told me it was
a really old lullaby.
[SERGEY]
Do you know all the words?
Just the one part.
Grandma told me
my mother also
used to sing it
to me a lot.
[SERGEY] Then let me
fill you in on something...
What's that?
Do you know the
rest of the words?
Nope.
It's just that your singing
is a little off key.
You'd be wise not to
sing in front of people.
I should--Ugh!
[ARIKA]
Idiot!
[SERGEY] It's very unlikely,
but just in case,
I had better prepare.
[MIYA] Man, I wish we could
be there to see it live!
[LILIE]
But we're not allowed.
We'll get the details
from our Big Sisters.
[MIYA gasps]
Look, it's the headmistress!
[YAYOI] And Big Sister
Shizuru is there too!
[IRINA]
Excuse us!
Professor Yohko!
Can we please watch
your television?
[ERSTIN]
Please?
No way.
You have a TV in your dorm.
[IRINA]
But it's too crowded in there.
Besides, we'll give you
something if you let us watch!
Ta-da!
I found it at
the antique store.
What do you think? Is it good
enough for your little darling?
Wow.
It's from way back.
Okay, but don't say
anything to the other girls.
Yay!
[OFFICIAL 3A] His Highness,
Emperor Argos the 14th
of Cardair Empire, accompanied
by "The Lovely Onyx,"
Lady Fia Grosse.
Welcome, Sir. This way please.
[SHIHO] Excuse me,
I was assigned to escort
the President of
the Aries Republic,
but her party
hasn't arrived yet.
I've been informed that the
president has been delayed.
Huh... It's so beautiful!
Use this opportunity to observe.
[SHIZURU]
The Otomes gathered here
are some of the most famous
and respected in the world.
I see!
Then who is the girl in white?
[NATSUKI] She's one of
the top three students
of the Pearl Class,
which is the sophomore
level at the academy.
The three of them
are called the Trias,
and they've been assisting
with the coronation ceremony.
Hey! She's looking this way!
Who, me?
[NAGI] Oh, so you're
here as a spectator?
[ARIKA]
Huh?
How confident,
despite your enrollment
riding on a dance-battle.
[ARIKA]
You're the guy from yesterday!
That's "Your Highness"!
[ARIKA]
Huh?
This is His Highness,
Nagi dai Artai,
the Grand Duke of Artai Kingdom!
[ARIKA]
Uh...
Um, thank you...
...for, uh, giving me
the chance yesterday...
Your Highness.
Arika, isn't it?
I don't think you
need to thank me.
Our own Nina has absolutely
no intention of losing to you.
I don't plan on losing either!
Hey, good answer!
An Otome needs that
kind of determination!
[chuckles]
[NAGI] This whole coronation
ceremony is a big joke.
I mean, we still
don't really know
whether dear little Mashiro
is a real princess or not!
Your Highness...
This isn't the time or place.
I guess everybody here
is pretending to forget.
[NAGI] Don't they remember what
happened 14 years ago?
Princess, you're so beautiful!
[MASHIRO]
Obviously! Let's go.
You stay here, Mikoto.
[MIKOTO meows]
[trumpets playing]
[CROWD gasping]
What a change!
Show respect!
Hear me, Princess Mashiro
Blan de Windbloom.
Are you prepared
to serve your people,
and sacrifice your
personal happiness,
for the sake of this nation?
I am.
In that case, I hereby
grant you this crown.
[ARCHBISHOP 3A]
All hail the new queen!
[applause]
[SHIZURU]
Are you ready?
I will use my GEM to control
and materialize your Robe.
[ARIKA]
Thank you so much!
[ARIKA gasps]
It's all right.
Here I go.
Materialize.
[ARIKA gasps]
Oh!
[MASHIRO]
Well, what a change!
You had better
fight a dance-battle
worthy of my
coronation ceremony!
After all, that's
the only reason
I granted you this chance.
[applause]
[MASHIRO] In celebration of
my ascension to the throne,
we hereby present
to you a dance-battle
between two Otome candidates!
[applause]
So which girl do you think
will win the dance-battle?
I hope they both lose.
Nina's favored to win, but...
But you think
there'll be an upset?
Oh, it's just a feeling I have.
[STUDENTS cheering]
At last, it's starting!
This should be good.
Do your best, Nina!
Both of you, listen.
Show me your best
performance and dance power!
Begin!
[ARIKA yelps]
[ARIKA]
Whoa...
[ARIKA screams]
[CROWD chattering]
Nina's incredible.
But so is Arika.
Shizuru! Shizuru?
[SHIZURU]
That's far enough.
Would you be one of
those poor people
who follow the Black Letter?
Are you dancing to their tune?
[RAD] Do not associate me
with those Schwartz fools.
[SHIZURU] Well, then,
who am I addressing?
[RAD] A messenger
from the Black Valley.
My goodness.
Such disgraceful rudeness
in front of a lady.
Since you don't have an
appreciation for elegance,
I'll have to teach you.
Materialize!
[RAD] Huh! The Bewitching
Smile Amethyst, is it?
You will be a worthy opponent!
[ARIKA yells]
Arika's doing quite well.
I suppose so, for a rookie.
[ARIKA yells]
[ARIKA screams]
[NINA] There's a chance
you might be the successor
to the Blue Sky Sapphire.
And if that's really true...
--[NATSUKI] No!
--[SERGEY] Not that!
I can't afford to lose to you!
[MASHIRO gasps]
[ERSTIN, IRINA gasp]
Grandma told me...
"If you give up, it's over."
And so...
[LILIE]
Does she still plan to fight?
[MIYA]
Maybe that girl is strong...
Well...
This is the place where
all my dreams are.
That's why...
...I can't let myself lose!
[NINA]
Huh?
[RAD]
You're good.
How about this?!
[ALL gasp]
Queen Mashiro!
Quick! Nina!
Come protect His Highness!
[CROWD screaming]
E-Everyone! Run! Go!
[ARIKA]
I have to save them!
I have to!
[NATSUKI] Episode 4 is next.
I got a bad feeling about it.
[ARIKA]
Why's that?
[SHIZURU] Because when
Natsuki was a student,
her underwear--
[NATSUKI]
Gah! Shut up, Shizuru!
[SHIZURU] Don't worry,
if something happens,
I'll cover it with my hands.
[NATSUKI]
That would also be a problem!
[ARIKA] Isn't anyone gonna talk
about what I'm going through?