The Sprites' Forest, huh?
If I could've avoided it,
I would have.
But considering the current
situation in Cardair,
I don't really have a choice.
[NAO]
Hm.
[MIKOTO meows]
Hey, you know, you really
do look like that fat cat.
[MIKOTO meows]
Huh?
[grunts]
[NAO]
Didn't I tell you to be careful?
--[NAO panting]
--[NATSUKI grunting]
Where the heck... are we?
[NATSUKI]
It's like a... black Garderobe.
Look at that.
♪ Mashiro's a demon! ♪
--Stop that!
--[ARIKA giggles]
I said, stop!
--[MASHIRO] Go away!
--[ARIKA] Mashiro!
You're always so
short tempered, Mashiro!
Lighten up!
Stop trying to be so friendly.
We've only just met!
Just met?
I've always been
watching over you guys!
[meows]
Always?
[yells]
[whistling]
Now commencing the stirring.
[MIYU]
Stirring complete.
[MAI]
You're always a tremendous help
when you come here,
Miyu. Now then...
[clanging]
Huh?
[MAI]
The food is ready!
Everyone come and get it!
Mai's food! Yeah!
By the way, where are we?
The Black Valley!
[MASHIRO]
The Black Valley...
The place Midori talked about
as Aswad's old homeland.
But I don't understand this.
I heard that the Black
Valley had disappeared
during the War
of the Twelve Kings.
Hey, Ari...
[BOTH]
Ah!
Seconds please!
It's like two Arikas...
Two Mikotos...
You always have a
fantastic appetite, Arika.
Hey, you two...!
[ARIKA, MIKOTO]
Seconds! Come on, hurry up!
[MAI]
All right! I'm getting them now.
[gasps]
[ALL but MIYU]
Ah!
So...
So what?
Just who are you guys?
Where are we?
And how did the two of us
end up here anyway?
Um...
Well, my name is Mai.
And this is Mikoto
the Cat Goddess.
Mai here is my servant!
Come on!
Would you stop that already?
[MIKOTO laughs]
And this...
This place is the Black Valley.
You two fell into it,
along with Miyu.
That's not exactly
what I meant...
Uh... That red
Gem on your ear...
I'm kinda wondering,
would it happen to be
the "Fire Stirring Ruby"?
Oh.
[laughs]
[MAI]
Well, yeah.
I knew it! Wow! Cool!
That means you're
the legendary Otome!
The tragic Otome,
torn between dreams and love...
[BOTH laughing]
Jeez. She sure doesn't
fit the image.
So then, you're saying
that this place
is really the Black Valley?
[MAI] That's right.
As far as the details go...
Uh... Miyu, you explain.
So I take it that the two
of you know each other?
[MAI] Yeah, she visits
me from time to time.
Arika, once, long ago,
this place really was
called the Black Valley.
Now, it is the holy ground
of lost technology.
The technology of the Otome,
and that of the Harmonium,
were both created here.
But now, the Black
Valley does not exist
in the usual sense.
It's a sealed valley
in a warp in space.
[MASHIRO]
A warp in space?
It was caused by the
power of the Harmonium,
used during the War
of the Twelve Kings.
[BOTH gasp]
[YUKINO] The situation has
to be confirmed immediately.
Send our Otomes to
Cardair if necessary.
We need accurate
information now!
Damn it, Nagi, you little runt!
Listen, Haruka,
I have a favor to ask.
Can you act as a messenger and
contact all the other nations?
I want you to tell them...
"Pursuant to Otome
Propagation Prevention
Agreement Clause C,
it is now Aries' intention
to hold emergency
deliberations."
So you're gathering
the heads of the nations
so you can warn them
not to do anything rash.
Sure thing.
I'll get them here even if
I have to drag them by the neck.
"Show the flag!"
Don't infuriate them, okay?
You need to persuade
them with kind words!
[HARUKA]
Hey, you're in good hands while
I'm in command of this moat!
[YUKINO] Uh, Haruka, I think
you mean "boat," don't you?
[MIYU] The Harmonium
can reverse the effects
of high-order
materialization sequences,
decomposing everything
and sucking them in...
Including this warped space.
Arika.
I believe you have already
seen for yourself
the organ beneath
Fuka Palace, right?
The song, the player
and the protector
now seem to be all in place.
Isn't that correct, Mikoto?
Well, my shadow
did get defeated.
It was by someone
with a black Gem.
A black Gem...
Don't tell me it was Nina?!
[MIYU]
The "Ultimate Black Diamond."
It seems that she's able
to take on both the roles
of the player and the protector.
The player?
[MIYU]
Yes. She can do that,
since she has the blood of
the Windbloom Royal family.
[gasps]
No... No way...
There's no mistake about it.
I know it's the truth,
because she was able
to start up that Harmonium.
How's she doing?
She's still sleeping.
Honestly, I didn't
think you'd recover
and wake up before she did.
It appears that using that
thing is quite exhausting.
Well, it took me
by surprise, too.
And to think I owe it
all to you... Sergey.
What do you plan on doing next?
What d'ya mean?
Regarding Nina!
And that Harmonium
in the basement!
Shouldn't that be
obvious by now?
Huh?
[knocking]
[SOLDIER 23A]
Excuse me, sir!
[NAGI]
Aries? Really?
That's great. I understand.
I'll head over in a minute.
Please tell me one
thing, Your Highness.
The casket of the
Valkyries' Predecessor...
Whose body is resting inside it?
I guess I can't hide it
from you any longer.
That's right. Inside it is...
Lena... You and...
that girl... I can't...
[MIYU] It was during the
rebellion 15 years ago.
I had made my way to
Wind City, but unfortunately,
I was too late.
However, as fate would have it,
I was able to
find Lena's daughter.
[MIYU] I picked up the
infant and carried her out
of Windbloom, then handed
her to your grandmother.
That child was you, Arika.
If so, that means I'm really...
Yes.
You are the only
daughter of Lena Sayers,
the "Blue Sky Sapphire."
My mother...
[gasps] Well, then,
how did the Gem...?
[MIYU] I found the Gem when it
was about to be sold to Artai,
and took it for safekeeping.
Then I gave it to your
grandmother to pass to you.
It is, after all,
rightfully yours.
Thank you, Miyu.
But I don't understand.
Why did you do so much for me?
Because, you are the blood
of my special person.
[tweets]
[clanging]
[meows]
We caught something!
Mai, be happy! Tonight's
dinner's arrived!
[MIKOTO grunts]
[MIKOTO]
C'mon, Jubei!
[meows]
Well, then, I guess
I'll go get some water.
Oh! I'll come and help you!
You're Miyu, right?
I, uh... I was wondering.
You seem to know quite a lot.
[MIYU]
I do not know everything.
However, it is true that
I have existed much longer
than any human has.
[gasps] Then do...
Do you know anything about me?
No, I do not.
I... guess you wouldn't.
I mean, why would you?
I'm only a replacement...
The Minister's replacement
for Nina. Nothing more.
I may not know your origins,
but do you know of the
story regarding the master
of the Pure White Diamond?
About the Otomes'
Predecessor, Fumi?
Every human has their own will,
and it is their will
that decides their fate.
A true leader or king is not
controlled by their birth,
but instead, rises by their
own will, lays down a path,
and does what needs to be done.
That is one conclusion
of many I have reached
through hundreds of
years of observation.
By the way, Miss Mai,
what was it that made you
wanna become an Otome?
I have a younger
brother back home.
He has a lot
of responsibilities,
which can be hard for him.
As his older sister, I felt like
I had to help him... or...
Well, something like that.
Miss Mai, please tell me!
What are Otomes, anyway?
Huh? Where did that come
from all of a sudden?
Now I see.
I don't really understand.
Why is it that Otomes exist?
What am I supposed to do?
[MAI]
Hm. Now that you ask...
Yes? What is it?
I don't know.
Say what? That is so not fair!
Come on.
Aren't you being unfair,
asking me all these questions?
[gasps]
Yeah, I guess I am.
[MAI]
Don't worry.
I'm sure that, one day,
you'll understand.
Or rather...
It's something only you
can understand, Arika.
But then, what if I make
some horrible mistake?
I'm still a fool,
so there's lots of things
I don't understand.
That's why...
That's why Ersty...
In that case,
what you have to do
is think it through
for yourself.
Decide on your own
what is best for you.
And if you think
you've made a mistake,
you can always start again
from the beginning.
Of course, some things can't
return to the way they were.
But, you have to believe
things will work out
for the best in the end,
otherwise you won't be able
to move forward.
[ARIKA]
Miss Mai...
I also had to think a lot
of things out on my own
after meeting with
Mikoto and Miyu.
I thought about why Garderobe
sealed its technology away,
and why Otomes existed.
That's the reason I decided
to stay with Mikoto.
But those...
Those are my own
thoughts and conclusions.
There's nothing wrong with
asking for other opinions,
but in the end, you've gotta
make your own decisions.
[MAI giggles]
Well, don't expect
to solve everything.
Start with what you can do,
then take it step by step.
Huh? You mean,
it's okay... to do that?
Of course!
If you strain your
brain too much,
you could end up
falling into a trap.
[ARIKA]
Hm.
[MAI] Trust me,
I speak from experience.
Now what? We won't
starve to death, will we?
[leaves crunching]
[BOTH]
Huh?
[BOTH gasp]
[NATSUKI, NAO scream]
[BOTH grunt]
♪ Big catch, big catch! ♪
[gasps] Headmistress?!
Arika!
It's you!
Queen Mashiro?!
You again?!
Natsuki?
M-Mai...
[sighs]
[NATSUKI sighs]
I really don't know
where to begin.
[laughs] You haven't
changed a bit, Natsuki.
Are you going to tell me
how you ended up here?
Before graduation, you left
a message and then disappeared
off of the face of
the planet. Not a word.
Do you realize how much
I worried about you?
I thought you'd gone
and died somewhere.
Me, died? You're kidding.
Then tell me, what did
happen to you, Mai?
[MAI] Well, I was feeling
really stressed out,
so I decided to take a
little trip. That much is true.
While I was walking around
and thinking about
what I should do,
I found myself surrounded
by a strange mist.
Then I got lost in this valley
and fell into the same
trap you guys did.
Okay, I can certainly
accept that explanation.
But then why are you still
holding the Fire Stirring Ruby?
You must have
a Master; who is it?
Huh?
Don't tell me...
[MAI] Yeah, it was a mistake
to bring the Gem along with me.
I fell into the trap, and then,
the Gem ended up in her stomach.
And it hasn't come back out?
[MAI]
Mm-mm. No.
In fact, we were somehow
able to enter a contract
under those conditions.
That doesn't make any sense.
It's because Mikoto
is the Crystal Princess.
Crystal Princess?
[MIYU]
Yes.
An Otome born under stricter
guidelines to maintain order
in this world, who possesses
"Otome-type Higher order
Materialization Powers."
Huh?
The Crystal Princess
is an original.
The last remaining pure wielder
of higher order materialization.
Who exactly are you, anyway?
I am Miyu.
I simply follow the
wishes of my lady
to watch over future
inhabitants of this world.
In accordance with those who
hold the fate of the Otome,
and the guidance of that star.
Nina.
You know, Father...
I really hated that girl.
But no matter how cruel
I was or how much I ignored her,
she didn't mind at all.
And then... before I knew it...
...I started to...
It's funny, isn't it?
I never cared for
friends. But then...
Don't let it bother you.
You were only following
orders, nothing more.
All of the blame for this
should be placed on me...
...and the Grand Duke.
But, Father...
[WOMAN 23A]
Meister Nina.
The Grand Duke
is calling for you.
Wait.
I'll go ask His
Highness to give you
a bit more time to recover.
Both you and His
Highness have a wish.
And if it can lead humanity
to a more glorious era,
it's my duty to do everything
within my power to aid you.
Nina.
Even if it means I have
to kill my friends.
Because I'm still an Otome.
I see. Shizuru's still there.
Yeah.
I understand that
she's been locked up.
She did that so I could escape.
I just hope she's not
being tortured right now.
Are you going?
[NATSUKI]
Yeah.
I've asked President
Yukino of Aries
and King Nguyen of Annam
to provide assistance
with appeasing
the other nations.
And when it comes down to it,
I am still the
Headmistress of Garderobe.
You sure have matured.
Shut up!
Well... I have a favor
to ask of you.
It's about those two.
I guess this makes
everything clear now.
I'm not the real queen.
I'm nothing more
than a replacement.
I know that you said
all those things
when we were in the Aswad
village... but now... I just...
Mashiro...
Lately, I can't
help but think...
Even if I reclaim the
country of Windbloom,
nothing is really gonna change.
But now, Nagi has the Harmonium.
If he can use it to truly
change this world
for the better, then...
Maybe he'll be able
to create a new world
without the need
for Otomes to fight.
[ARIKA]
No way! That's wrong!
Now, in accordance with
the Otome Propagation
Prevention Agreement,
begin the emergency
deliberations.
[door slams]
[SECRETARY 23A]
Madam President!
Albright Base is under attack!
[YUKINO, HARUKA gasp]
I noticed something
when Nina appeared
at the Dragon's Cemetery.
She was crying.
But I felt that it
wasn't just because
Sergey had been injured.
It was something even worse.
There are still lots of
things I'm confused about,
like if technology benefits us,
or whether Otomes
are good or bad.
That's why I've been
trying to think about
this stuff so much.
But I do know...
...that Nina is very
cute when she smiles.
I love it when Nina smiles.
I wanna see her like that again.
But that time Nina
was crying. And then...
[gasps]
[ALL]
Huh?
[ARIKA] Grand Duke Nagi's
making Nina do those things...
I can't agree with that!
I know that it's wrong!
Arika...
That's why... Mashiro...
[NAO]
Arika!
[MASHIRO, ARIKA]
Huh?
[MIKOTO] Just as I expected.
They used it again.
This is the country of that
woman who wears glasses.
In Aries? Damn that Nagi.
He's showing off the
power of the Harmonium
to the other leaders, and
forcing them to choose between
following him or fighting him.
At this rate, the world
will be split in two,
which will result
in a major war.
[ARIKA]
Nina...
[NATSUKI] We're leaving
immediately for Garderobe.
[BOTH gasp]
Oh, great.
We come all this way
just to turn around.
[BOTH]
We're going with you!
No, you won't.
You two are to
remain here for now.
[gasps]
[ARIKA]
Why?
Because you haven't
been able to unlock
the Gem's full potential yet.
You'll die if I let you go.
But...
Hey... What about a test?
Mikoto?
Huh?
Uh...
[ARIKA] So if I beat Mikoto,
then you'll let me go, right?
Can that girl really test Arika?
Even if I use my Robe,
I've never been able
to beat Mikoto.
What? Really?
[MAI]
Mm-hm!
[NATSUKI]
Her?
[yawns]
Then I'm not gonna hold back!
[yells]
[yelling]
[ARIKA screams]
What are you doing, Arika?!
Wha--?!
[MIKOTO] I have to say
that the black Gem girl
is a lot stronger than you.
[ARIKA]
Hmph.
[yelling]
[yells]
[ARIKA screams]
[ARIKA groaning]
[yelps]
Still wanna continue?
Mikoto... No...
Cat Goddess! Cat Boss!
Wait, no, Teacher!
Please, teach me how to
fight as well as you do!
Please!
Ha!
If you are Arika's Master,
and intend to remain
with her in the days ahead,
then there is one thing
I must ask you.
Do you think you can
reach... your goal?
I don't know.
But I swore to my citizens
I would, together with Arika.
Then learn your role well.
Become a queen worthy
of being Arika's Master.
Learn my role?
How am I supposed to do that?
How about taking some
lessons from Mai?
Huh?
[NATSUKI]
It's something she hid from me,
but Mai is the older sister
of the prince of Zipang,
Takumi Tokiha no Kami Tadayori.
She's none other
than Princess Mai...
Mai- Hime .
Hey, Mashiro. Please
wait a bit more.
I'll become a powerful Otome.
Then wars will be total history!
That's good. That's
really good, Arika!
[ARIKA]
Hm.
[MAI] Isn't this supposed to be
a steaming-hot school drama?
[NATSUKI]
Uh, we already did that.
[MAI] Oh, but I'm sure
Midori is really--
[NATSUKI]
We've already done that, too.
[MAI]
What?!
Come on! I'm finally
making an appearance and--
[NATSUKI] Poor girl.
There, there, don't cry.
[MAI] It's not comforting
when you do it, Natsuki.