[NINA]
Hmm...
[SERGEY] That uniform
looks really good on you.
[SERGEY] Congratulations on
being accepted, Nina- chan .
[NINA giggles]
[NINA]
Thank you very much.
I guess one day you'll stand
before me like this in a
beautiful wedding dress just
as I'm about to give you away.
But I'm never going
to get married! Ever!
I mean, I can't get married
once I become a Meister Otome.
That's why... uh... I...
I will always be your daughter.
And I'll never leave
your side, Father.
Is that OK, though?
[SERGEY] Of course
it's okay... Nina- chan .
[alarm buzzes]
[WOMAN 23A] Meister Nina, it's
time for the Royal Conference.
[CHILD 24A] Wow!
That's so awesome!
[MAN 24A] That's the fleet
of Remus' Imperial Guard.
[CHILD 24B] Look! That ship's
the Antoinette, from Florince!
[MAN 24B] More and
more Otomes and Kings
are coming to Wind City.
I wonder if this means all
those rumors are really true.
About the war, you mean?
What is His Highness thinking?
--Shh!
--Huh?
Oh yeah, you never
know who's listening.
All right, why don't
we get started?
Report on the current situation.
Of course. Just now,
King Charles of Florince
and his Meister Rosalie
have arrived in our nation.
They are about to sign
the treaty of alliance
with our government
very shortly.
This is all thanks to
the many demonstrations
of the Harmonium's power.
The deadline given by His
Highness is quickly approaching.
It will be interesting
to see how many nations
withdraw from the old treaty
and come over to our side.
[NINA]
What is Cardair's position?
[SMITH] They seem to be
focused on arguing over
the selection of the next heir.
I'm not surprised,
given every one of the
candidates has been eliminated.
[NAGI] How scary.
Still, for the most part,
things are going as expected.
But the actions taken by Aries
are very troubling,
Your Highness.
It could be fun if they
decide to come at us.
Well, if they do,
I'm counting on you, Nina.
Of course. Leave it to me.
[HARUKA] Why can't we
take the Suzushiro?
All that we need is the
ceremonial equipment, right?
Yes, but the problem is that
our usual imports of goods
from Remus have suddenly been
cut off. I'm guessing that Remus
has decided to side
with Grand Duke Nagi...
Damn that opportunistic hag!
How dare she go and betray us
at a time like this! Huh?
[SECRETARY 24A ] Madam
President. You have a guest.
Come in.
[HARUKA gasps]
Long time no see...
Big Sister Haruka.
[HARUKA]
Sara Gallagher?!
[YUKINO]
One of the Five Pillars,
the Milky Way Aquamarine!
But... I thought you were
supposed to be doing some work
with those dudes in the east!
You mean the "Eastern Kingdoms"?
How many times do I
have to remind you?
Please be precise with
your actions and comments!
Never mind.
I have some good news. Today,
I've brought some nice presents
for you, all the way
from Zipang.
[HARUKA, YUKINO]
Presents?
[MARIA] Laula Bianchi.
Rosalie Claudel.
Oh my goodness! Miss Maria!
Big Sister Yukariko!
Hello there!
[LAULA]
Good to see you again.
[YUKARIKO] I see. So your
wedding was cancelled
because of that
incident with Akane.
Yep, that's how it turned out.
And the girl who was supposed
to replace her went missing,
along with the Spiral Spin
Serpentine Gem.
As a result, I had no
choice but to reenter
a contract with this
Abyssal Jade gemstone.
You were telling me
you were relieved
to get out of the marriage
because it was political.
Aw, don't tell them that,
Big Sister Laula!
Stop being so mean to me!
]You are really not taking this
seriously enough, Rosalie.
This is completely different
from what we experienced
with the Lutesia
border conflicts.
This time, we might end up
having to kill each other.
Maybe even Carla,
and Big Sister Haruka...
[NINA] However... that is
what makes us Otomes.
All of you will be
under my authority.
Please follow my orders.
Very well. I will do as you say,
Ultimate Black Diamond.
It is only natural. I don't want
to see another city disappear.
Please show these two
to their quarters.
I will speak
with you both later.
[MARIA]
Wait a moment, Nina Wang.
[NINA]
Hm?
[MARIA] This is for you.
We found this
when we were collecting
Erstin Ho's possessions.
[NINA]
Huh?
[MARIA] It's a letter addressed
to you and Arika Yumemiya.
[TOMOE] So, how does
it feel to order around
all those prominent
Big Sister Meisters?
And not just that. What does it
feel like to control a weapon
that's said to have once
destroyed half the world?
It's nothing. I do what I do
because it is necessary.
For the sake of
your dearest father?
To make the Grand
Duke's ideals reality!
To change this twisted world...
[TOMOE]
Liar.
Hm. Just do whatever
you want to do.
Right now, you're able to make
any wish of yours a reality.
Even if you want a man,
there are plenty of loopholes
you could use.
For example, you can...
Shut up, right now! What would
you understand about it?!
I don't think you could!
I don't even want to understand!
You do nothing but make excuses
to hide the fact that your
jealousy is out of control,
killing your two best
friends in the process!
I suggest you leave...
Get out of my sight right now!
Hm. You know something, Nina?
I'm looking forward
to the war beginning.
From now on, let's both watch
our own backs, all right?
[TOMOE]
Nina is so mean.
I'm sure I didn't do anything
to make her angry like that.
That's a magic spell
to relieve the pain.
Ah! Please, just wait
a little longer.
If I have a bit more time,
I'm sure I can convince them
to set you and the
Headmistress free.
Don't worry about that.
Everything's all right
now that I have you,
my dear Tomoe.
Oh, Big Sister...
[IRINA] Headmistress,
it worked like a charm!
It took a bit of doing, but...
I was able to get that letter
to Big Sister Shizuru!
[various cheers,
affirmative reactions]
I see. Good.
[IRINA] And regarding
that other thing...
What did you find out?
Is it possible?
Yep, I'm almost
certain it is!
It's exactly the same as the
data left by Professor Yohko.
[NATSUKI]
Good job.
[IRINA] I can't
take all the credit.
My classmates also helped a lot.
And as for using the computer,
this book really came
in handy in the end.
It was something
Erstin left behind.
I see.
Any word from Aries?
They sent a message to report
their departure was delayed
by a few days, but they promised
they'll be here on time.
Mm. All right. Everyone, begin
your preparations as planned.
[various affirmative responses]
[MIYU]
My lady...
[MIYU] The ones who have
inherited your blood
have grown up to be
healthy and strong.
Now it's time to do what I must.
[indistinct murmurs]
[MIDORI]
How's Rad doing?
[GAL] Not good.
Although I repaired his body
as best I could.
[RAD] Looks like this form
has reached its limit.
Still, we're fortunate that
our battle against Cardair
only cost the lives
of Lumen and myself.
[MIDORI]
But Reito...
[RAD] Midori. We knew
what would happen.
I'm already dead.
Now I can finally...
--[YOHKO] Not yet!
--[RAD] Hmm?
[MIDORI]
Yohko...
I won't accept it. I don't want
to lose you a second time.
Reito.
[NINA]
Ersty...
[ERSTIN] Dear Arika and Nina.
By the time the two of you
read this, chances are
I will already be gone.
[NINA]
[ERSTIN] I've always known
that a day would come
when I would have
to fulfill my duty.
And so I forced myself
not to get close to anyone.
I purposely kept myself from
making too many friends.
But then I met you, Nina...
and later Arika too...
and I got to know everyone in
my class. I had a lot of fun.
I was hoping that the black
letter would never come to me,
and that I could remain together
with everyone forever. But...
[ERSTIN] I really don't know if
serving the God of Intelligence
and taking back the power of
science is a good idea or not.
But I can't bring myself
to go against it.
Ever since I was a child,
I've been brought up
to believe that it's
the right thing to do.
[ERSTIN] I'm sure you can both
make your own decisions.
Because you're both very strong.
[ERSTIN] I really loved both
of you. I was very fortunate
to have been with you and
have both of you in my life.
Nina, Arika... there were
many things I couldn't say,
but I wanted to
say... I'm sorry.
But I can say thank you.
Thank you so much...
[NINA] "...for being my
most precious friends.
Love, Erstin Ho."
[NINA weeps]
Oh, Ers... I'm not strong...
I'm not strong at all.
What you went through...
[NINA weeps]
[SERGEY]
Nina...
Nina, what's wrong?
Why did I do such
terrible things to my friends?!
Ersty... I made you...
and Arika...!
[SERGEY]
Nina!
Get a hold of yourself, Nina!
That's not even all of it...
I killed them. All those people.
[SERGEY]
That's enough!
That's enough, Nina.
I'm here.
[NINA]
Father...
[NINA sobs]
[SERGEY]
Have you calmed down?
Yes. I'm sorry. I, uh...
Stop forcing yourself.
I'll go have a word with
His Highness. I'll convince him
not to ask you to use
that damn thing ever again.
[SERGEY] If that doesn't work,
I'll protect you
and think of a way for you to
escape from him. So that way...
[NINA]
That's impossible.
[SERGEY]
Huh? Ah...
[NINA] You understand that more
than anyone, don't you, Father?
It's just that the one
person most important to me
is suffering... And yet I...
I can't do anything about it!
[SERGEY groans]
[NINA]
Then...
Then, please... take away
my right to become an Otome.
That's crazy!
How could I do that?
[NINA]
You're right.
It couldn't happen.
Because I'm not...
'Cause I couldn't
become your blue star.
[SERGEY gasps]
Ah, Nina...
You'll be... my father?
Let's play, Father!
Thank you very much, Father.
[NINA]
Sergey...
[NAO]
So, enjoying the scenery?
Nao, maybe you can help me
figure something out.
What do you think? About
the existence of us Otomes.
Huh? Why the sudden
deep thoughts?
We're a necessary evil.
I thought you'd say that. Here.
Huh?
[NAO]
Hm?
[NATSUKI]
The "Break String Spinel."
That's the Meister Gem
I set aside for you.
[NAO] You mean you had this
on you all this time?
I'll admit, there were times
when you really pissed me off.
But on the whole, I'm actually
very thankful to you.
I was only able to get
this far because of you.
[NAO] The proper payback for
those who barge in and take away
our home is to let them
experience some physical pain.
Even if that person happens
to be Grand Duke Nagi.
Whatever you say.
I won't argue.
[SERGEY]
Lena...
Ever since that day,
I've been chasing after you.
It was like running after a star
that I would never reach.
[SERGEY] I was lured in by His
Highness's unstoppable will...
I believed there was
nothing in this world
that His Highness
couldn't get his hands on...
And that's why I...
[gunshots]
But from now on,
that's all over.
[SERGEY]
I have finally realized...
I've finally realized
what's most important to me.
[SMITH] That would be most
troublesome, Major.
And here you were the trusted
friend of His Highness!
I never dreamed that you
would attempt such a thing.
[SERGEY] It's because I'm His
Highness' friend that I must
right the wrongs
he plans to commit.
No one wants to plunge this
world into war and chaos.
We have to stop it.
[SMITH] Chaos?
But chaos is perfectly fine!
It's the force of life
that makes people
compete with each other
and move forward.
Without chaos,
we are merely stagnant.
Are you truly happy
living in this world
of artificial limitations?
I'm happier to live in this
world than I would ever be
in a world where
I have to sacrifice
the people most important to me.
[SMITH]
Heh!
[gunshot]
[SMITH]
No... way...
Don't worry, Smith.
I promise I'll make sure
to bury you along with
your precious Harmonium.
[gunshot]
[SERGEY gasps]
[SERGEY]
Your... High... ness...
Well, that's really quite
a shame. Sorry, Sergey.
[SERGEY]
Nina...
Father?
[knocking]
[SOLDIER 24A]
Miss Nina! Come quickly!
Something's happened
to Major Wang!
[NINA gasps]
[NINA] This... This can't be...
Father? Father!!
[NAGI] It seems he had
a gunfight with Smith.
[NAGI] It really is
a terrible shame.
[NINA]
Father!!
[NAGI] He's suffered
massive brain damage.
He's still breathing,
but not for much longer.
[NINA] No! Father!
You can't die!
But Nina, there is
still hope for Sergey.
[NINA]
Huh?
You can use this Harmonium!
As the ultimate weapon,
this thing is capable of putting
a warp in time and space.
If you wish, it will give you
the power to stop time before
Sergey has stopped breathing.
And then once we open
Garderobe's forbidden library...
and use the power that's
been sealed inside...
it should be possible to
bring Sergey back to life.
So, dear Nina. Tell me.
What is it that
your heart wishes for?
[NINA]
I...
[NATSUKI] People.
The day has finally arrived.
Today is Nagi's deadline
for a final answer.
We must find a way to put
an end to his ambitions
and free this city and its
people. We hereby commence
"Operation Garderobe
and Wind City Liberation"!
A message from
the resistance headquarters!
"Otomes will dance."
I repeat, "Otomes will dance."
Then launch the signal flares!
[SOLDIER 24B]
Hm? Three red signals?
Ah! It's a declaration of war!
[siren]
All units, take level one
combat positions!
Engines, maximum output!
Main tank blow,
up trim thirty degrees!
[NAVIGATOR 24A]
Aye, up trim thirty degrees.
Here comes the ultimate desert
Dreadnought, the Suzushiro!
Let's go! Begin surfacing!
[soldiers wail]
Ah. They're coming.
[ROSALIE chuckles]
[TOMOE]
Ah.
[HARUKA] Okay now, let's get
this show on the road!
Extend the battle decks!
Unlock the cannon launchers!
And open fire!
[NINA] Sergey...
For your sake, I am willing
to make the entire world,
and everyone in it, my enemy.
Well, it's started.
Are you ready to do this, Nina?
[NINA]
Master. I am ready.
[MAI]
You're going, aren't you?
Huh? You're going?
[ARIKA]
Yeah.
[MAI sighs]
[MAI] But you guys haven't
finished training yet.
Yes, but out there,
everyone is taking part
in this battle to win back
my nation. So that's why
I have to go. It's my duty
as Queen. Right, Mai?
[MAI] Of course.
You're quite right.
[MIYU]
Arika. You must realize
the full scale of
what you will face.
Many different Otomes,
the "Ultimate Black Diamond,"
and the Harmonium will all
be standing in your way.
Knowing all this,
do you still wish to go?
That's the reason I'm going.
Mashiro and I have to create
a nation where everybody
can live happily.
Right now, that's the
dream I'm fighting for!
[MASHIRO]
Hm.
Don't worry about it! You both
have been working really hard!
I know you can do it!
[ARIKA]
Hm!
[MASHIRO]
Hm.
[ARIKA]
So wait for me... Nina.
[MAI]
You're going, aren't you?
[MASHIRO] Yeah. Everyone's
fighting to win back my nation.
[MIKOTO] Then let me teach
you my ultimate attack!
[ARIKA]
Yes, Master!
[MIKOTO] The cat in the
sky turns three times!
[ARIKA] Awesome!
I'll definitely win with that!
[MAI]
Are you sure you wanna go?
[MASHIRO]
Yeah, maybe not...