[sighs]
[ARIKA sighs]
[BOTH]
Huh?
What's wrong?
Aren't you gonna say something
like, "Wow, it's so jiggly!
It's just like Erstin's boobs!"
or something weird like that?
No. I don't feel
that hungry anymore.
[NINA, ERSTIN, IRINA gasp]
[IRINA]
Well, this is a major event.
Arika has lost her appetite?
What's next?
Snow in the forecast?
[ARIKA groans]
Wait, that's...
What is it?
[IRINA gasps]
[NINA] That's Big Sister
Akane and Kazuya,
the son of the Krau-xeku
family of Cardair.
Are you sure it's them?
Yeah, maybe it's someone else.
Here, look through these.
[IRINA]
Uhh...
Well, whatever.
Big Sister Akane is
Pearl Number One.
She's not gonna
make any mistakes.
[ARIKA]
What do you mean, "mistakes"?
Don't make me explain.
[ARIKA]
Hmph.
Meanie.
[screams]
[growls]
How dare you, Arika!
[ARIKA screams]
--I'm sorry!
--Stop right there!
Those two really have
become good friends lately.
Uh, yeah...
Kazu...
Akane, it's no use. I can't
hold back anymore. I...
Kazu, what're--?
[AKANE]
Stop, stop.
No, you mustn't.
No!
[gasps]
I'm sorry. Please forgive me.
To do this to someone
aspiring to be a Meister...
I should be the one apologizing.
I'm sorry... Really, I am.
But, Akane.
[AKANE]
Sorry. Sorry. I'm really sorry.
[MARIA]
Akane Soir.
[AKANE gasps]
Were you listening to me?
You have an important guest.
Please go to the Headmistress'
office immediately.
Uh... Yes, right away.
Uh! You want me to
become a Meister?
I'm sure you must be surprised
at the sudden request.
King Charles' Meister,
Rosalie Claudel,
is getting married and
will therefore be retiring
from her Otome position
in a short time.
Big Sister Rosalie
is getting married?
You have been selected
to inherit the "Pure
Heart Malachite,"
the Gem which
traditionally serves
the Royal Family of Florince.
But I'm still a student,
so how can I--?
This decision is
not unprecedented.
We're making the
exception for you
because of your
special abilities.
[OFFICIAL A] We have already
contacted the Soir family,
and your parents were
especially pleased.
Congratulations, Mademoiselle.
Or rather, Meister Akane Soir.
[YAYOI]
Awesome!
Isn't it great news?
To be chosen as a Meister
while still a student?
That's the first time I've
ever seen it happen!
I hear the Palace of
Florince is magnificent!
Oh, how wonderful!
Irina, Erstin,
you're on Big Sister
Akane's room duty, right?
Have you heard anything else?
Uh, no.
We haven't seen her
since hearing about this.
Is it about Kazuya?
Well, yeah.
Cardair and Florince
have never had
a good relationship
with each other.
What do you mean?
It's not something you
need to know about, Arika.
[ARIKA]
Oh... All right.
[NINA]
Huh?
[CHIE]
Congratulations!
You've reached your dream
before everyone else.
Let me give you my blessings.
Thank you very much, Chie.
But truthfully, it all seems
too surreal right now.
What's up with you?
If you wanna brag,
now's the time, so go ahead!
Well, Akane, it'll be tough
not having you around,
especially when there're
problems like we had
during the survival test.
We'll be fine!
After you're gone,
I'll be able to guide our
underclassmen properly.
[sighs]
What's wrong with me?
Why do I have this heavy
feeling in my chest?
Huh?
This is...
Hey, Arika, are you
feeling any better?
[gasps]
Hey, that's mine!
Did you look?
[NINA]
Hey!
[ARIKA]
How did I get here?
Oh, looks like you're awake.
I don't get it. Why am I here?
You fainted suddenly, remember?
[ARIKA]
Mh-hm.
I was quite surprised.
Out of nowhere,
Nina burst in carrying you.
Nina carried me?
[YOHKO] She said you
were acting strangely.
She thought maybe the
nanomachines went haywire.
What's wrong?
Is something bothering you?
Uh, Professor Yohko?
[YOHKO]
Hm?
And that's how it is.
Am I really sick, Professor?
Well, your nanomachines
are fine, but you are sick.
[ARIKA yelps]
According to an old saying,
it's a sickness not
even god can cure.
Am... Am I gonna die
from this sickness?
In some cases,
you may go through pain and
suffering even worse than dying.
Grandma, I'm... I'm gonna...
Hey, do you know the story
of the Fire Stirring Ruby?
Let's see...
Ah! Here it is!
Which one?
[IRINA] Biographies of
Otomes , chapter 109:
"The Legend of the
Fire Stirring Ruby,
hersorrowful soul wandering
around the Sprites' Forest."
Wow...
Is this story really old
enough to be a legend?
No, this is a story from
just a few years ago.
They say during that time there
was a very exceptional Otome.
Everyone had great hopes for
her future, and it was decided
that she would inherit
the Fire Stirring Ruby
when she graduated the academy.
But unfortunately, she had
also fallen in love with a man.
She had already decided
which Master she would serve
even when she first enrolled,
so she found herself torn
between choosing love
and choosing her dreams.
Then, on top of all that,
our great predecessor
singled her out
to become one of
the Five Pillars.
Huh? The Five Pillars?
Wait a minute,
you mean like the Headmistress
and Big Sister Shizuru, right?
[NINA]
That's right.
They are Otomes who
serve our predecessor
instead of an ordinary master,
and protect the
existence of Otome.
It's a highly
respected position.
But it only made
the decision harder
for the Fire Stirring Ruby.
She had to think long and hard
about which path
she would choose.
So she went into
the Sprites' Forest,
where the future-telling
god resides.
But in the end, she never
emerged from that forest.
People sometimes
say that her soul
is still wandering inside
that dark forest.
[TOMOE]
She was very foolish.
All because she loved a man.
What do you mean?
Falling in love with a man
goes against the principles
of being an Otome.
That's why Garderobe
places so much emphasis
on bonding with our Big Sisters.
After all, we can always develop
a feeling of love from that.
We've received intelligence
on that man from
Schwartz, John Smith.
He was last seen in the
vicinity of Artai's borders.
Shizuru, can you go
and investigate?
Of course, Natsuki.
If that's what you wish.
Thank you.
Although truthfully, I'd prefer
to have you remain here,
more than ever.
[ARIKA]
The Fire Stirring Ruby...
Why did Professor Yohko want
me to know about that story?
[NAO]
So, what're you gonna do?
[AKANE]
There's nothing I can do.
I knew this would
happen someday.
If you leave the school,
then I'll be raised to the
number three position.
That'll turn my life
into a big hassle.
I'm really sorry, Nao.
I've always been pushed by
everyone to become a Meister,
so I did my best to
achieve it, and now--
Man, stop trying
to be so perfect.
Why don't you do
what you wanna do?
Go ahead and give everything up.
That's impossible.
Both for Kazu and myself.
Ah, forget it. I guess
that's not your style.
Me, a Trias? Ugh... What a pain.
[ARIKA]
Don't!
Arika?!
[AKANE]
Arika, can I ask you a question?
Have you ever fallen in love?
[ARIKA]
Hm? No, I haven't.
Love is such a
mysterious thing.
Before I ever met him,
I had no idea that he even
existed out there in the world.
But now even just a
single word from him
can bring me such joy
or such sorrow.
Somehow, just thinking about him
can make my heart feel so tight
that it becomes painful.
Why...?
Why... do we fall in love?
[NAGI] So, the song, the player,
and the protector...
[SMITH] Those seem to
be the requirements
for activating the Harmonium.
This looks interesting.
Seems like having you
find the real Princess
was worth the price
I had to pay.
By the way,
there's one more thing.
Thanks to the data we've
gathered about this,
and the lost technology
of materialization,
we can now create something
that's very close to
the original structure.
Stop flattering yourself.
So, is it usable?
[SMITH] Of course it is,
Grand Duke Nagi.
You will learn of its
abilities very soon.
Thank you!
[KAZUYA]
Akane!
[AKANE] I'm sorry I asked you to
come out here all of a sudden.
Hey, I'm happy to see you.
[AKANE]
Uh...
[TOMOE panting]
[SHIZURU]
Huh?
Big Sister Shizuru... Um...
I heard you'd be leaving
the school for a while
because of work.
So I... So I--!
Time sure flies by.
I guess you'll be becomin'
a Pearl pretty soon,
won't you, Tomoe?
[TOMOE]
Big Sister... I...
You remind me of the
way I was a long time ago.
That's why...
That's why I'm tellin' you
not to get distracted.
Keep your focus on what's
ahead of you, all right?
I must be goin' now.
[ARIKA]
Miss Shizuru!
I'm just heading off
to work right now!
Then allow me to accompany
you for part of the way.
Sure!
Are you going out?
[SHIZURU]
That's right.
What?!
I'm sorry... Kazu.
You can't do that!
I love you, Akane, and I
thought you loved me too!
I do love you, very much!
But I can't...
I just can't give up my
country or my dreams!
Isn't it the same
with you, Kazu?
Don't you wish that someday
you'll be able to
serve your country?
Isn't that why you
study so hard?
Won't you be late for work
if you continue walkin'
with me any farther?
Um...
Miss Shizuru, I was
just wondering,
have you ever fallen in love?
[gasps]
[ARIKA gasps]
Miss Shizuru?
[ARIKA whimpers]
Keep workin' hard, Miss Arika.
Wait, Akane! Please, just wait!
[BOTH]
Huh?
Akane, just listen to me.
[ARIKA]
Big Sister Akane!
[AKANE, KAZUYA gasp]
What is that?!
It's a Slave!
[PEOPLE screaming]
[SHIZURU]
I'll take care of this.
You two better leave, quickly!
[AKANE]
Uh.
Kazu...
[SHIZURU]
Hurry, you must go!
I'll stay!
Please let me fight with you!
Do you know what it'll mean
for you to fight now?
Yes. But I still am an Otome.
Very well.
Materialize!
Akane!
[SHIZURU]
I'll leave the Slave to you
while I go look for its owner.
There are too many people...
[AKANE grunting]
[gasps]
[AKANE screams]
Akane!
I have to become an Otome.
I have to become a Meister!
That is my wish.
That's what I've worked
so hard to achieve!
It's always been my
dream... That's why...
Big Sister Akane.
Akane.
I have to!
[yelling]
[screaming]
It's coming!
It seems you're usin'
a different gemstone
from the ones before.
Mind if I take a look at it?
[growls]
I guess it's too late.
It appears you have been
consumed by the stone.
In that case...
[PEOPLE screaming]
No! Kazu!
[gunshot]
[gasps]
[screams]
[AKANE]
Huh?
Goodbye, Kazu.
Big Sister Akane!
Why aren't you stopping her?!
You're supposed to be in
love with her, aren't you?
Aren't you?!
[KAZUYA]
I do love her!
But... sometimes things
are just impossible!
But--!
Hm?
That's enough, Arika.
It's between the two
of them, remember?
Only they can decide what's
most important for themselves.
[PEOPLE chattering]
Anything wrong?
[ARIKA]
Mh-hm.
It's just... something...
[NINA]
Hm?
Well... I'm not sure myself.
[MARIA]
Silence, please.
We shall hereby commence the
Meister inauguration ceremony.
[trumpets blaring]
[NATSUKI] Pure Heart Malachite,
Meister Akane Soir.
[AKANE]
Yes.
If you pledge to
accept this man,
Charles Guinel Roy
d'Florince as your master,
and swear to protect his life
and devote yourself entirely
to him as his Otome,
then give to him the contractual
gemstone in your hands,
and by doing so,
bind yourself to him.
From now on, I'll take
special care of you, Akane.
[AKANE] This is what
I wished for... so...
[door opens]
[KAZUYA]
Wait just a minute!
[PEOPLE gasping]
It's him!
[OFFICIAL A gasps]
Kazu.
I still care for you,
Akane! I love you!
For you, I'm willing to
renounce everything!
My family, my country...
everything!
And so...
Come with me, Akane!
[CHARLES]
Huh?
Who is this annoying young man?
[AKANE]
I'm sorry, Your Majesty.
That man...
...is the reason I can't
become... your Otome.
[CHARLES]
Huh?
Big Sister!
[ERSTIN]
[PEOPLE chattering]
Wow, that was cool!
Someone! Stop those
two immediately!
That's right!
Such rude behavior cannot
be tolerated. Stop!
[OFFICER A yelps]
Let's go!
[AKANE]
Yes!
I'm so glad for
Big Sister Akane!
Ahh...
That was really
something, hey, Nina?
[SERGEY] To give up your
dreams for love, huh?
That's one way of
living your life.
Is that something you envy?
No! I will definitely
become a Meister Otome!
Without fail!
Is that so?
Well, go for it, Nina- chan .
Yes. Thank you, Father.
And how about you, Antsy?
Huh? What, me?
Uh... Well, I...
[AKANE] I gradually find myself
thinking more about that person,
and now just a single
word from him
can bring me great
joy or sorrow.
I guess it's too soon for
you to worry about that.
Little Antsy's got some
growing up to do.
[AKANE]
Somehow, just thinking about him
can make my heart feel so
tight that it becomes painful.
Why... do we fall in love?
No way!
Tell me it isn't true!
[phone ringing]
[NATSUKI] What can it
be this late at night?
What?!
[YOHKO] We've received a
transmission from Shizuru
using a heavy particle signal.
It's the Romulus
and Remus border.
A battle's taking place
between their Otomes?!
[explosion]
[ARIKA] So if I fall in love,
I can't become an Otome?
[IRINA] It's more like if you
do stuff because you're in love.
[ARIKA]
What stuff?
[IRINA]
Erstin, you explain!
[ERSTIN]
Sure, let me demonstrate.
Mm. Oh, Irina...
[IRINA]
W-Wait a minute! Erstin! Ah!