[ARIKA humming]
[ARIKA]
Ahh!
It all starts today!
The first step towards
my dream! All right!
Good morning!
Isn't it a beautiful day?
[groans]
Time to wake up, Nina!
[NINA]
Just five more minutes...
No way! Come on! Wakey-wakey!
Hurry up and get
outta bed, all right?
Wake up! Come on, Arika!
It's time for morning clean up!
Huh...?
Do we really hafta clean for
a whole hour every morning?
[ERSTIN chuckles]
Finally, time to eat! Yum!
[STUDENT A]
Big Sister, you wouldn't believe
what happened
in class yesterday.
Everyone's talking about it.
[IRINA]
Good morning!!
Good morning!
And good morning to you, Irina!
Your first day at the academy!
The classes are pretty tough
here, so ya better be prepared.
[ARIKA]
Hm.
But I'm looking forward to it!
[bell tolling]
[TOMOE]
Stand up!
Miss Yukariko,
please teach us well!
[STUDENTS]
Please teach us well!
[NAGI]
I hope we're not troubling you
by barging in like this.
No.
But in the future, it would help
if you let us know beforehand.
Oh, of course, this
city has telephones.
I'd forgotten about that.
It must be nice being surrounded
by so much technology.
This is the classroom
for the Coral Star class.
[SHIZURU]
Headmistress!
Excuse us for a moment.
Are you absolutely
certain about that?
Yes.
Apparently it's been put on sale
at the store called "Backstage."
[NATSUKI sighs]
[MARIA]
Headmistress.
[BOTH]
Huh?
[NATSUKI]
Miss Maria.
Have you already heard about it?
It appears that something
has suddenly come up.
Perhaps we should
take our leave now.
Sir.
[STUDENTS chattering]
[IRINA]
How's it goin' so far?
I don't get any of it.
Come on, cheer up!
Our next class is Phys Ed.
You're really good
at that, aren't you?
Yep!
Did you remember to
bring your gym clothes?
Of course!
Uhh...
Mm...
Arika? What's the matter?
I feel like I've
forgotten something.
[STUDENTS gasp]
[YAYOI]
Big Sister Shiho!
Arika!
You're that maki-maki girl!
[ARIKA yelps]
Shut your mouth.
Arika, how could you do
such a terrible thing?
[ARIKA]
Uhh...
[SHIHO] You have to
come with me right now.
[ARIKA]
What? Hey! What is it?
Hm?
Now, Arika, this is
your uniform, isn't it?
[gasps] Of course! That's it!
I was trying to remember what
it was I had forgotten today!
Thank you.
That's so kind, to go to the
trouble of bringing-- Huh?
Ah!
What's this?
What happened to it?!
Your little act
isn't fooling anyone.
You sold this uniform to that
shady and despicable store
called Backstage, right?
Despicable? What?
[CHIE]
Hmph.
Ah, yes, that store...
[SERGEY]
You're aware that Otomes
are idolized in many nations,
and are extremely popular.
[NAGI]
Seems that way.
Well, Backstage is a store
that sells merchandise
to diehard Otome fans.
Ah, and you're saying that store
somehow got a hold
of Arika's uniform?
It seems that's
what this is about.
Word is that the really rabid
fans collect that sort of thing.
Items like genuine uniforms
and gym clothes
can be traded for
ridiculously high prices.
Interesting.
But that girl couldn't have
anything to do with it, right?
Unlikely. Because that girl
comes from the border lands.
I doubt she's even aware her
uniform could be sold there.
From the border lands, huh?
Hey, I guess that
means she has no
ties to any of
the nations, right?
[SERGEY]
None. And no relatives, either.
Well then, maybe I
should be her patron.
[gasps]
Uhh... I would think
twice about that, sir.
She may have the skills
to fight a dance battle,
but her chances of becoming
a full-fledged Meister are slim.
Oh?
Well, if that's what you think,
I won't consider it any further.
[ARIKA]
What?!
There's no darned
way I'd do that!
Watch your tongue!
Your language is far too rude
for addressing a senior!
It's one thing to bend the rules
and get into this academy,
but you have no
money to pay tuition!
Uh! Well, that's true,
but... but...
Hey. I don't hafta
listen to this!
What gives you the
right to lecture me?
[AKANE]
I'm sorry, Arika.
As the top three students
of the Pearl Class,
we're known as the "Trias,"
and it's our job to provide
guidance to the students.
Therefore, I must ask you,
where was the last place you
saw this uniform yesterday?
It got dirty last night,
and I wanted to
wash it right then,
but I ended up forgetting
it in the laundry room.
She's obviously lying.
[gasps] That's not true!
I know I might not
have a lot of money,
but I would never do
something like that!
There's just no way!
Stop playing innocent!
How did it end up in that store?
Are you suggesting someone
stole it just to frame you?
[ARIKA]
Huh?
[SHIHO]
Sure, it makes sense
that other students think
you don't belong here!
It's inappropriate
for a girl like you,
without family or support,
to attend this academy!
But that doesn't mean--!
[MARIA]
Stop this immediately.
[NATSUKI] We'll take care
of everything from here on.
[SHIHO gasps]
[MARIA]
We will handle this matter
with more fairness and
discretion than you will.
But, I...
You disagree?
No!
[NATSUKI]
Read this.
It's a letter from an
anonymous individual
who has expressed a
desire to support you.
Apparently, this person was
helped by your mother
many years ago.
By my mother?!
[NATSUKI]
Mh-hm.
It's your choice whether or
not you accept the offer,
but if you do, I imagine you
would no longer have to deal
with so much slander
and unfounded suspicion.
Arika Yumemiya.
For now we'll set
aside the facts
of how your uniform
came to be sold,
but you are still responsible
for not taking care
of it properly.
Do you understand this?
Yes.
Then until the case is resolved,
you will be confined
to the dormitories.
You are hereby
suspended from classes.
Arika sold her uniform?
That's what I heard!
I think that's why Big Sister
Shiho dragged her away!
[LILIE]
No way!
Uh, but come
to think of it,
yesterday she was talking about
needing to make some money.
[YAYOI]
So that's why!
[LILIE]
Mh-hm.
[TOMOE]
Stop it, everyone.
Even if she's new,
she's still our classmate.
We should believe her,
even if no one else does.
Oh boy. This is serious.
Well, if that's the case, Nina,
maybe you shouldn't
spend so much time
worrying about that Arika girl.
Besides, she might be
crushed very soon.
[ERSTIN]
What should we do, Nina?
We do... nothing.
If it's true, then she'll be
kicked out, simple as that.
What a harsh outlook!
[MASHIRO]
What?!
That little brat?!
Yes, it's something about
her selling her uniform.
It's the talk of
the school right now.
I gotta act on this now!
[AOI] Miss Mashiro,
where are you going?
Well, duh! The academy!
You can't!
Until you finish this, I'm not
letting you out that door!
[growls]
[CHIE] I feel kinda
sorry for that girl.
Judging by her reaction,
I doubt she's ever experienced
this level of teasing.
I was just doing my job
as a member of Trias.
Yes, there is that too.
So, what do you think?
We oughta do something,
right, Akane?
Yes, that's right.
[ARIKA] "Many years ago, I was
greatly helped by your mother.
It is my fond wish
to repay her kindness
by providing you, her daughter,
with support at
Garderobe Academy.
Do not worry about
paying me back.
Please take advantage of my
offer to achieve your dreams.
I hope you will become
as wonderful an Otome
as your mother was."
[sighs]
[ARIKA]
Mother.
Is it really all right for me
to believe this person?
[SHIHO] Are you suggesting
someone stole it
just to frame you?
Sure, it makes sense
that other students think
you don't belong here!
It's inappropriate
for a girl like you,
without family or support,
to attend this academy!
--[door opens]
--Huh?
[ARIKA]
Nina.
Can I ask you something?
Do you think...
people really hate me?
Ya know, this is the first time
I've ever been to a real school.
And I was looking forward to it.
But now... I'm thinking...
...maybe I shouldn't
have come here!
[NINA] If you truly think that,
you should hurry up and leave.
I thought you wanted to become
an Otome no matter what!
That's why you challenged
me to a dance battle,
even though you had
no chance of winning!
But...
[growls]
I guess that's as
far as it goes.
Nina...
[SERGEY]
Even if you somehow win,
you'll be crushing
the dreams of Nina,
who has endured strenuous
training to enter the academy.
Is your dream really
worth that much to you?
[ARIKA]
I finally found my dream.
So I'll keep chasing
after it, no matter what.
That's right!
[ARIKA]
Ersty! Irina!
Arika! Thank goodness!
We were worried about you.
I swear I didn't
sell my uniform!
So I hafta find out
how this happened!
Please, you gotta help me!
Uh. Sure!
Of course!
Ahh!
Thank you!
[CHIE]
Well, in that case...
[AKANE] ...we might be
able to lend a hand.
Big Sister Akane!
[NINA growls]
What's wrong with that girl?
She's such an idiot!
[yelps]
Big Sister Nao?!
[NAO]
Quite an outburst.
What's up? Something wrong?
I have to ask you for a favor.
[MARIA] Permission to leave
campus? Both of you together?
Yes, ma'am.
We already have permission
from Big Sister Akane.
Very well, then.
If Pearl Number One accepts
responsibility for you,
I'll allow it.
[IRINA, ERSTIN]
Thank you very much!
[ARIKA gasps]
[IRINA]
Don't make a spectacle!
You're already
breaking two rules
by leaving the dorms and campus!
But still!
Wow! It's the latest MP4 model!
[KAZUYA]
Hey, are you Akane's juniors?
Yes!
[KAZUYA]
Uh.
Um... where is she?
I'm sorry.
Something urgent
came up at the school
and Big Sister Akane
couldn't make it.
[KAZUYA]
Oh, is that so?
I'm a good friend of Akane's.
My name is Kazuya Krau-xeku.
I'm in second year at
Windbloom University.
It's nice to meet you!
So, the person who came to
the store to sell it was a man?
Yeah, he told them
that he'd found it.
But the store clerks don't
remember his face at all.
Now, about the uniform.
Was the torn apron mended
by someone in the store?
Yeah, that's what I hear.
And apparently it was so dirty
that it had to be washed.
[KAZUYA chuckles]
Usually prefer not
to wash such items.
Anything else?
[KAZUYA]
Hmm...
The clerk said, "Not again!"
[BOTH gasp]
Then somebody else went to him
and asked him the
same questions?
[MAN A chuckles]
Nothing like an
unexpected payday.
Quite a rare and valuable find.
Now this is what
I'm talkin' about.
[NAO]
Hi.
[MAN A growls]
[NAO] Looks like
you're in a good mood.
Whatcha do that for?
You got paid quite a lot for
a Garderobe uniform, wasn't it?
Who the hell are you?
[NAO] You've got nerve
making trades on our turf.
Did you think you'd get away
with it, my dear "brother"?
[NINA]
Huh?
[gasps] Juliet!
[MAN A screams]
Thank you so much
for all your help.
We're sorry we troubled you.
[SERGEY]
Huh?
Oh, don't mention it. I'm happy
to do whatever Akane asks of me.
And since it was my first time
in that kind of place,
I learned a lot.
Bye now!
[ALL]
Thanks for everything!
[SERGEY]
I'm not impressed.
Future Otomes
on a date with a man?
Good afternoon, Major Wang.
[SERGEY]
Hello, Erstin, Irina.
Thanks for always
looking out for Nina.
What are you doing here?
Oh? You seem to be a bit
down about something, Antsy.
Oh that's right,
didn't you sell your uniform
to pay your tuition?
I'd never do such a thing!
[SERGEY] But I hear you
don't have any relatives
or financial support.
Wrong! Guess again!
There is someone who's decided
to help me out after all!
Oh? Who is this weirdo?
I'm sure he's a very kind
and cool person, unlike you!
Well, I suggest you
study hard, then.
You don't wanna let such
a nice person down!
[ARIKA] I don't need
you to tell me that!
[AKANE] Is that so? I'm sorry
he couldn't be of much help.
[CHIE] Well, I guess there
wasn't much we could do.
After all, it takes experience
to force information
out of the sort of people
who go to those stores.
[groans]
At this rate...
[MASHIRO]
I found you!
I heard you did
a major screw-up
on your first day
in the academy!
It's you.
Your Majesty!
You came all the way
out here to say that?!
You bet!
I'm here to laugh at you!
[laughing]
Miss Mashiro.
I should share this with Mikoto!
Where is she? Bring her to me!
Uh... if it's that cat
you're talking about...
Hey. That handkerchief...
Ah! So then, last night...
That's it!
I've solved the mystery!
And the culprit is...
The pet of Queen Mashiro...
Mikoto the cat!
What did you say?!
[IRINA]
Last night, during dinner,
the cat was present when
Tohika mushroom soup
was spilled all over
Arika's uniform.
Tomoe's handkerchief
also got soup on it
when she helped to clean up.
This is that handkerchief!
Mikoto's favorite food
is Tohika mushroom.
It's right, isn't it?
[MASHIRO]
Uhh... Uh-huh.
[IRINA]
So last night,
the cat found the
mushroom-covered uniform
that Arika left in
the laundry room.
And when Mikoto was taking
it away, she dropped it.
This is nothing but
your imagination!
[IRINA]
Check this out!
The tear on the uniform
is irrefutable proof!
You all saw how the
same kind of tear
was made on the handkerchief.
That place is
probably on the route
Mikoto always takes on her way
back to the State Guest House.
And then, someone found
the uniform, picked it up,
and sold it!
In other words, how the
uniform went missing
and how it was sold
are entirely unrelated!
And that is the truth
behind this matter!
So there you have it,
Your Majesty.
All lies! Mikoto would
never do such a thing!
Mikoto! Wait a minute!
[MASHIRO]
Uh...
Ugh! Nothing but lies!
You're all
disrespectful riff-raff!
These are all false accusations!
They have to be
'cause I say so!
That means there's
no mistake about it!
[NATSUKI sighs]
Well then, Arika.
It seems that the
conclusion of this incident
is in the hands of Her Majesty.
Right, and I think it's
clear to everyone now
that I did not sell my uniform!
And thanks to all this,
I became friends with people
who never stopped
believing in me.
So I've decided.
I don't know who
wrote this letter,
but I'm gonna believe in them.
Is that so?
Yes!
And that is how it all ended!
Really? Wow!
The cat was behind it?
But that's good news.
If one of the students
had been behind this,
there would've been
all sorts of trouble.
[TOMOE sighs]
Irina, Ersty, thank you
both so very very much!
And you too, Nina!
For... well, you know!
Oh please, I didn't
do anything for you.
And I don't ever plan to.
What a meanie.
[ERSTIN, IRINA chuckle]
I feel bad putting Queen Mashiro
and Mikoto on the spot.
But hey, the whole
thing's wrapped up now,
so it's probably for the best.
[NINA]
If this scares you,
then I suggest you never do
anything stupid like this again.
I don't intend to tell anyone,
but if you continue to go
out with men like that,
you're only going to get burned.
Uh... What are you
talking about?
I can't stand anyone who
pulls dirty tricks like that.
If you ever do it again,
I won't forgive you.
[screams]
[MARIA]
That was quite a show.
And you, agreeing with that
absurd investigation.
[NATSUKI] Just let this
one go, Miss Maria.
And then there's this
anonymous supporter.
Isn't it a little rash
to accept that?
[sighs]
At the moment, the only
leads we have about Arika
are the Blue Sky Sapphire
and that individual.
We have to take advantage
of any and all opportunities.
No matter what
his plans may be.
[MIYA]
I'm sorry! But...
[TOMOE] I told you
to tear her uniform up
and leave it on her desk.
But what did you do?
You wanted to make
some pocket money.
[MIYA] I... I thought it would
make a lot more trouble!
Besides, I just couldn't
rip up a uniform like that!
That's why...
Ah!
I'm sorry! Next time--
Next time I'll do it right!
[ARIKA]
This mushroom soup is delicious!
[MASHIRO]
It's Tohika mushroom,
a special variety from
the "big breast" family.
Nicknamed the Mai-mushroom.
Ah, how sad. The poor girl,
reduced to a fungi!
[MIKOTO]
I'm just as happy as ever!
[ARIKA]
Who just said that?
[MIKOTO meows]