[TECHNICIAN 25A] The Valkyrie
Core has been destroyed!
The Slaves under our control
have been destroyed!
The Valkyrie Unit has
stopped functioning!
Well, looks like it's game over
for us. Then let's finish it all
by turning this city
into a wasteland.
You understand, right?
There's no turning back
for either of us after
everything that's happened.
[NINA]
Sergey...
You've been a kind man.
Too kind.
But right now I am thankful for
the kindness you showed me.
[NINA] You allowed me
to retain my powers.
So for your sake...
I will do this!
The Harmonium!
Nina...
Look, the sun!
It's being covered in darkness.
Let's go.
Materialize!
[SARA, SHIZURU, and NAO]
Get outta here. Nagi is serious
about demolishing the city.
No!
We're not leaving!
Both of us made a promise.
I'm going to create
a nation where everyone can
live in happiness and peace.
So I'm not gonna run away again.
My mind's made up.
Mashiro, I'm gonna need you
to entrust your life to me.
I don't know how
I'm gonna do this.
But I have to at least try.
Somewhere, Nina is crying out!
[NINA]
Arika...
[MASHIRO] My life is
one with yours, Arika.
You're my Otome.
Now let's do this!
[ARIKA]
Hm.
Huh?
[MASHIRO]
You guys...
Don't overdo it! Even though
you've gained the power
of the Sapphire, it's
impossible to do this alone!
Give us a chance
to help out, okay?
[MIKOTO]
Hm!
Jeez, how'd I get this
hard labor so soon?
Thank you!
[MIYU] She has earned the
true powers of the Sapphire,
and a Master who will
walk the path with her.
My Lady. The moment has come for
me to fulfill your last wish.
Now, Guiding Star, it's time!
Is that...? It can't be!
To think... that
legend was true.
[YUKARIKO]
Hm?
They say that when the
Guiding Star shines red...
All the Otomes will be released
from the shackles
of their contract.
[STUDENTS gasp, murmur]
[HARUKA]
What...?
All right! Miyu has
finally done it!
Yeah.
[HARUKA]
Huh? What?
[MIYU]
Hear me, Otomes.
Allow me to free you
from your burden of fate.
Huh? The Robe activated
without the contract!
[MIYU]
Choose for yourselves.
By your own will,
decide what you must do.
[YUKARIKO gasps]
No need to tell me. I made
my decision long ago! Let's go!
Unh?
[SHIHO]
We're on our way!
[HARUKA] Huh? Hey!
Wait for me, you guys!
Rosalie!
Well, Big Sister Natsuki,
we thought you could use a hand,
so... here we are!
Yah!
Hngh!
Huh! Your Majesty!
Please allow all of us Otomes
to serve under your command!
But why?
We were asked to
choose for ourselves.
And I believe there's a clear
choice of what we need to do!
[IRINA]
Hang on, we'll help too!
--[YAYOI] Me too!
--[LILIE] Yeah, and me!
Please, hurry!
We'll do our best to
keep this under control.
All of you...
Very well. I'll leave it
up to you, Otomes. Let's go!
Our mission is to take back the
castle and stop the Harmonium!
Jeez! I told you to wait for me!
So unfair. They're playing
against the rules, you know.
[TECHNICIAN 25A] There's
another fleet approaching
from north of the city!
What? It's Cardair!
Looks like I no longer
have a way out.
All right, then activate
all the original Slaves.
[SLAVE-MASTERS] Under the
contract of darkness,
I fulfill my oath to you.
God of the ancient light,
knowledge, and wisdom,
grant me a loyal servant.
Don't worry, I'll handle these.
You and the others go
into the castle, Natsuki.
Thanks, Shizuru.
Good luck.
Like I always say, an Otome
needs strength, skill...
And guts, right?
Correct!
Now, let's settle this
competition once and for all.
We'll see which one of us can
defeat more of these guys!
You haven't changed one bit.
Yeah! Come on!
I'll turn you all
into demon fish fry!
I don't even know what
you're trying to say, Haruka...
Uh, Madam President?
It's nothing.
Right... Here, Major Hallard.
Thank you. I'll be
returning to the castle now.
Ha!
Arika! We're leaving
Nina up to you!
Right!
[SHIHO] Red maki-maki, blue
maki-maki, yellow maki-maki...
[SHIHO squeals]
[SHIHO laughs]
You're not even using
your Robe's powers.
Way to go, swirl-head.
Why don't you just
shut up, Juliet?!
Hehe... Huh?
[NAO and SHIHO]
Huh?
[SHIHO] Big Sister Mahya?!
Of the Five Pillars?!
[NAO] Akane?! Wait, how come
you're still an Otome?
[AKANE]
Hmph!
[NAO and SHIHO]
Uh?!
[AKANE] We were
always being chased.
And then, just when
our moment came...
Kazu was taken away to become
the next emperor of Cardair,
and I was captured
by Big Sister Mahya.
[MAHYA]
You mean I arrested you.
At any rate, I agreed
to drop all charges as long
as she entered into a contract
with His Highness Kazuya.
I never willingly
agreed to this.
I'm not gonna let you do "that"!
And I'm not gonna
give up, either!
I'm staying outta this...
[MARIA]
Honestly...
[ALL]
Huh?
[MARIA] Even after all these
years, you still lack grace...
Headmistress.
[NATSUKI]
Huh?
Don't tell me...
[NATSUKI]
Miss Maria?!
How pitiful. I made every effort
possible to age gracefully,
only to have to appear
in this form again?
[indistinct grunting, shouting]
[SAKOMIZU]
Go!
[CHIE]
Aoi!
[AOI]
Huh?
[CHIE]
Thank goodness...
[AOI]
Oh, Chie...
So they're even down here...
Listen, Arika. You must
go now. You must go
and release the young player,
Nina, from the Harmonium.
And be sure to hurry.
Playing that organ
for a long period of time
is very dangerous.
[ARIKA]
Hm.
[MIKOTO yells]
[TECHNICIAN 25A]
We're detecting a Robe
in the underground passage!
It's the Blue Sky Sapphire!
Nina...
Arika.
[NAGI]
Welcome.
Hi, Mashiro.
Nagi.
Nina, please!
Stop this already!
I can't. If I stop
the Harmonium...
[ARIKA gasps]
If I stop, Father will die.
Father was willing to do
anything to protect me,
even sacrifice his own life.
So that's why, this time...
I will risk everything and
everyone to protect my Father!
But... he might say...
No... I know...
I know exactly what
Sergey would say!
He'd say he'd rather die than
make you do all of this!
What do you know?!
The things between
Father and me...
How could you ever understand?!
[ARIKA yells]
Arika!
Arika...
[NAGI chuckles]
Over there.
[ARIKA] I can understand
a little bit...
Because, Nina...
I also... loved Sergey.
When I first realized
my true feelings,
I couldn't think about
anything or anyone else.
I didn't even think about
what you were feeling.
Then you should understand!
Even if I sacrifice everything,
even if it were in exchange
for the entire world...
I would still want only him!
[NINA yells]
Then... I have to stop you,
Nina, no matter what it takes!
Nina... Arika...
All we can do is watch
over them from afar.
Everything is in
their hands now.
[NAGI] How ironic. In the end,
the future of the world
still depends on a
fight between Otomes.
Of course, I understand that
the contracts have been broken,
so all we can do
is watch and wait.
No. I'm not just
going to sit back
and let Arika fight on her own!
Stop the Harmonium, Nagi. Now.
Impossible. In case
you hadn't guessed,
that thing only listens to Nina.
She is the real princess.
I'm just trying to revert
this world back to the way
it originally was. This business
of sacrificing Otomes
and sealing up technology...
It's strange, don't you think?
But that's...
Don't worry about it. Sure,
it's true that this world
has been destroyed once
because of this thing...
[ARIKA yells]
[NINA yells]
But this time, I'll be
supervising it carefully.
That way, there'll be
no mistakes.
But that's no good! That's
not gonna change anything!
Then what do you suggest?
Keep things the same?
No! Technology will be
released gradually!
I'll make sure in the future
Otomes won't be necessary!
But I can do all those things by
myself! I don't need your help!
Yeah, right.
You could never manage that.
--[MASHIRO] Shut up...
--[NAGI] Huh?
Shut up! It can be done!
I believe in it!
[ARIKA and NINA grunt]
Why are you still
fighting? Tell me!
I made a promise!
We have to create a nation where
everyone can live happily!
That's nothing but
a farfetched dream!
It is a dream.
But it's because of that...
When I first came
to this city...
When I first met you, Nina,
and saw Miss Shizuru...
I thought, "I really
wanna become an Otome!"
And you know, I did
just that, and here I am.
But if I hadn't had that dream
of mine during that time,
I would never have been able
to become an Otome like this.
You have to believe in dreams
even if they're impossible.
Actually, you gotta try to
make your dreams come true,
or nothing will happen!
You think that way because
you've never been torn apart,
or made mistakes that
are too hard to bear.
That's not true, Nina! If you
make a mistake, just think hard
about how to fix it and start
again from the beginning!
Then just hold your head
up high and move forward!
But... it's too late!
For everything!
[ARIKA gasps]
[NINA yells]
[NINA] Why?! Why do you
always keep on fighting?
Why do you never give up?
Well, because
I love you, Nina.
I love everybody on this planet.
That's why I can never
give up, no matter what.
I'm a fool who
doesn't know anything.
But I really want to learn
as much as I can about you.
So please, let's start from the
beginning again, as friends.
Okay, Nina?
[NINA] I should've talked more
openly about so many things...
With Erstin... and also...
with you, Arika.
It's not too late, y'know.
Let's start again, Nina.
Ari... ka...
[MASHIRO gasps]
[NINA screams]
[ARIKA]
No, Nina!
[MIKOTO] This is bad.
It's gone wild!
If this continues, it's gonna
be a repeat of the last time!
[NAGI] It's too late. The
Harmonium has been constantly
working to keep Sergey alive.
It's about to exceed its limits.
What did you say?!
The Harmonium's
powers and memories
are now flowing into Nina.
It won't be long before
there's nothing left of her.
[NINA screams]
[NAGI] It's sharing the
mistakes humanity has made
because of that thing.
Fear, hatred...
and most of all, despair.
It's like what
happened to the Gem
once known as the
Pure White Diamond.
This same despair
caused it to turn black.
Damn you...
[NAGI] I thought I could
wrap everything up before
it came to this. But it seems
my gamble didn't pay off.
Ah well, what can I say?
Why don't we all just
die together, then?
[ARIKA]
Nina! Ahh!
[NINA screams]
Arika! You have
to kill me! Please!
[ARIKA shudders]
[NINA]
You have to...
If you don't kill me now,
this world will be destroyed!
I can't!
Please, Arika...
I'm begging you...
If you think of me
as your friend...
[ARIKA screams]
[MASHIRO]
Stop her, Nagi! Ahh!
[NAGI] Nothing you do's
gonna change anything.
Quiet, you!
[MASHIRO cries]
I told you that it was useless.
Shut up! I'm not
about to give up.
[MASHIRO cries]
[MASHIRO] We are
never gonna give up.
Isn't that right, Arika?
Yes, Mashiro...
That's right.
[ARIKA yells]
Nina...
Arika... Thank you...
[ARIKA]
Nina...
Nina!!
[NAGI]
Huh?
Nagi!
Oh crap!
[NAGI]
Ah--!
Nagi Dai Artai. By the authority
of the emergency council,
I hereby place you under arrest!
[NAGI sighs]
Hurry! Take him to
Garderobe right away!
[STUDENTS]
Yes!
[NATSUKI] All because of
something like this...
[MIKOTO] You do not
belong in this world.
[ARIKA grunts]
There, I finally
caught you, Nina...
Arika...
[NAGI chuckles]
[NAGI]
Eh?!
[MIKOTO]
Hmm...
[NAGI cries]
[MASHIRO] Today I
pledge to my citizens
that I will fulfill all
the promises I've made.
[applause]
All right! It's time
for the finishing touch!
Okay! Just leave it to me!
[ARIKA wails]
[murmurs]
You really haven't
changed at all, have you?
[ARIKA chuckles]
Sorry, my mistake! I'll get
it right this time. Here we go!
[murmurs]
The castle's done! Finally.
[MASHIRO]
Mm-hmm.
[MASHIRO] I know it might look
a little bare right now...
but this... is the
place I begin anew.
[MASHIRO] Yes, this is
just the beginning.
For me, and for all of us.
Isn't that right... Mimi?
So, let's get started, Arika!
[ARIKA]
Mm-hmm!
[ARIKA] My dreams
are all right here.
So keep watching me!
[ARIKA]
Ersty... Nina...
[SERGEY groans]
Who are... you?
My name's Nina.
Just plain "Nina."
Nina...
It's nice to meet you, Sergey.
[SERGEY] Sergey...
That's... my name?
[NINA] It's okay, we'll take
it slowly. There's no rush.
Another chance...
for both of us.