[MINISTER A] Princess Mashiro,
you are the true successor
to the Kingdom of Windbloom
and its throne.
Everything in this
country is yours.
[gasps]
[MASHIRO]
I want that doll!
[PEOPLE]
Yes, Miss Mashiro!
[MASHIRO giggles]
[MASHIRO]
I hate this kinda flower!
[PEOPLE]
Yes, Miss Mashiro!
[MASHIRO giggles]
[MASHIRO]
Be my horse, Sakomizu!
[SAKOMIZU]
Yes, Miss Mashiro!
[MASHIRO]
Giddy-up!
[SAKOMIZU neighs]
[giggling]
[WOMAN A]
Princess!
[WOMAN B] Miss Mashiro!
It's time for your studies!
[MIKOTO meows]
[WOMAN A]
I've had it with that Princess.
Both the King and Queen were
decent, honorable people,
but she's nothing like them!
[WOMAN B]
You're right.
Maybe the rumor that's
going around really is true.
[WOMAN A] Hey, you shouldn't
be talking about that.
[WOMAN B] You can't blame me
for wanting to believe it.
I think it's true.
I bet the real princess was
with the King and Queen
when it happened.
[MASHIRO]
He's from Artai?
[WOMAN C]
Yes, he's the duke.
[NAGI]
Hi there. Are you Mashiro?
[MASHIRO]
Yes, I am.
So you're the one people
have been talking about.
Did you know everyone's calling
you the fake Princess?
[gasps]
How... dare you...
[WOMAN A]
She doesn't even resemble
the late King and Queen at all.
[WOMAN B] That could
mean the rumor is true.
[MASHIRO]
Stop!
[WOMAN A]
So, the real Princess...
[WOMAN B]
...together with her parents...
[WOMAN A]
...actually died.
[NAGI]
Fake Princess.
[MASHIRO]
Stop!
Stop it!
Was that because of you, Mikoto?
Were you giving
me nightmares? Jeez!
[meows]
Hey there, Mikoto.
I really am the Queen.
I am the Queen of Windbloom.
Aren't I?
[MIKOTO meows]
[ARIKA]
"Dear Sir. Today is our day off!
It's my favorite
day of the week.
Since we don't have
morning cleaning today,
we all get to sleep in a little.
But even if it's a day off,
hardly anybody can
afford to take it easy.
Some people train.
Other people study.
Some students help the teachers.
And others clean their
Big Sisters' rooms.
There are so many things to do,
and everyone seems really busy.
Oh, what about me?
Well, actually, I've started
working part time.
I know you told me not
to worry about money,
but I still feel I'd like to
pitch in as much as I can.
I plan to pay off my
debt to you bit by bit.
Big Sister Nao introduced
me to the job.
Can you guess what it is?
Everyone says this
job is perfect for me."
[WORKER A]
Hey, young lady!
We're all supposed to
meet up at the front gate
when our break is over.
[ARIKA]
Okay!
"That's all for now, Sir!
I'm off to work!"
[CHIEF A]
Hey, you guys!
Listen up, okay? Today,
we have a very special guest.
Queen Mashiro has come
all the way out here
to personally compliment us!
[WORKERS applauding]
Ugh.
[MASHIRO] Everyone, I am
counting on your hard work
so that this will become
a magnificent castle.
You came to observe
this all of a sudden.
But remember,
this is not Garderobe.
Therefore, you must
be very cautious.
Yes, yes, I know. Huh?
[WORKERS chattering]
[ARIKA]
Uh...
[chuckles]
How is that girl handling
the work so far?
Oh, her?
She might be small,
but she works really hard.
She's got a lot of potential!
[MASHIRO]
Oh, is that so?
Keep doing your best,
for my sake.
[MASHIRO laughing]
[growls]
Boy, did ya see? The Queen
is even cuter in person.
I'm gonna brag about
this to my mom later.
What's with her?
Acting so innocent...
[CHIEF A]
Hey, young lady!
Can you come down here?!
'Kay!
[CHIEF A]
Hm?
Oh, there you are!
Let's see. There was a letter
for you at the office.
I picked it up for you.
Oh.
[gasps]
[CHIEF A]
Is something wrong?
Uh! Thank you very much!
[CHIEF A yelps]
[ARIKA]
What did you need me for, boss?
[CHIEF A clears throat]
Uh, I want you to
take some things
to the castle's inner garden.
[AOI sighs]
[AOI] Well, at least
this section seems
to have come through undamaged.
Isn't that right, Miss Mashiro?
Huh?
Miss Mashiro?
You're the one they're all
calling... the fake Princess.
[grunts]
Miss Mashiro?
I've decided.
Restart the construction
from scratch.
We shall rebuild this castle
into something completely new.
[AOI gasps]
[ARIKA]
What?!
[MASHIRO]
It's you!
How can you say
that at this stage?!
You're just gonna put all the
work we've done to waste?!
Be quiet!
You're talking to the
Queen of this nation!
What's wrong with doing
things the way I like?
Everything is wrong! You're
only thinking of yourself!
It makes me wonder if
you're even a real Queen!
[gasps]
[slap]
[MASHIRO]
Of course I am.
How dare you.
I really hate you!
[ARIKA]
Huh?
Miss Mashiro!
[NAGI] Oh boy. Looks like
you've done it now.
I haven't had the chance
to see her lately,
so I decided I should stop by.
But what I get is a
very interesting scene.
Heh.
[ARIKA]
A fake Princess?
[SERGEY]
Yeah.
It's a rumor that's been
kept alive for many years.
[SERGEY]
Here, try using this.
Huh? Uh. Thank you.
An Otome's appearance
is important. Be careful.
After all, you don't
want to look any worse
than you already do.
Mind your own business!
[MAN IN BLACK A]
How 'bout over there?
[MAN IN BLACK B]
No sign of her.
[MAN IN BLACK A] Ugh! Where in
the world could Her Majesty be?
[MAN IN BLACK B]
Keep it down.
[MASHIRO]
Father... Mother...
[SERGEY]
It happened 14 years ago.
Fuka Palace was invaded
by a group of rebels.
Both the King and the
Queen were killed.
To make matters worse, the
Otome who served the King
had just retired
prior to the attack.
No one was strong enough
to stop the rebels.
[ARIKA] You seem to
know a lot about this.
[SERGEY] Back then, I was
here as an exchange student.
During the attack, the infant
Princess went missing.
But just when people
were giving up hope,
the Minister of Interior
Affairs at the time
found the girl who we
know as Queen Mashiro.
He proclaimed her
the surviving Princess.
The only evidence
the minister had
was the confession of a
criminal he'd captured.
He has since passed away, and
the Princess is now the Queen.
Everyone pretends to
have forgotten about it,
but that rumor will
never go away.
That's terrible.
If you truly want
to be an Otome,
you'd better think hard about
who you want to serve.
Once you enter into
a contract-- What?
Hey, Antsy!
[ARIKA] I'll wash this and
return it to you later!
[SERGEY]
Hmph.
[MASHIRO]
I hate them all.
They're all making fun
of me behind my back.
[NAGI]
There you are, Mashiro!
[MASHIRO]
Hm?
Nagi?!
Oh man! I was looking
everywhere for you!
What do you think
you're doing here?
[NAGI] Aww, don't make
such a scary face!
I have something very
important to tell you today.
[growls]
[NAGI]
Hm.
[grunts]
Uh? What?!
[NAGI] Your Majesty,
Mashiro Blan de Windbloom,
Queen of Windbloom Kingdom,
I ask you, will you grant
me your hand in marriage?
Whoa...
Amazing!
No! There's no time
for that! Um, now...
Which way should I go? Hm?
[ARIKA]
That's a blue gemstone!
Hm?
It can't be...? Can it?
[MIKOTO meowing]
[ARIKA]
Huh? Wait, you're her cat!
Hey, hold on!
What?!
Wh-Why are you asking me
that all of a sudden?!
[NAGI]
Take it easy.
You like me too,
don't you, Mashiro?
No way! Who would like
a jerk like you?
I've hated you for as
long as I can remember!
Ever since the first
time we met!
Oh, that time.
I'm so sorry! I was nervous!
But that was because
you were so cute.
[gasps]
L-Let me go...
or I'll call for help.
I'm not letting you go.
I've had a crush on you
for a long time now.
I've liked you ever since
I first laid eyes on you.
Please don't...
[ARIKA]
Wait a minute!
[BOTH gasp]
[MASHIRO]
You again?!
Stop!
You're not supposed to force
people to do stuff like that.
That's what Grandma told me!
[MIKOTO meows]
[NAGI]
Huh?
Uh! Mikoto!
[MIKOTO hissing]
[sighs]
You've made your point.
I guess I'll give up this time.
I'll see you later, Mashiro.
And you too, Arika.
[thud]
Oh, are you okay?
Hey!
Yes, of course I'm okay!
I-I don't need your help.
Come on.
[MIKOTO meows]
[ARIKA, MASHIRO yelp]
[ARIKA, MASHIRO scream]
[SAKOMIZU]
You still haven't found her?!
[MAN IN BLACK B]
We're very sorry, sir!
Well, that's Miss
Mashiro for you.
You can't beat her in a game of
hide and seek in this castle.
Don't be so casual!
What if something has
happened to her?
You know that there've been
people targeting Miss Mashiro.
Even before her coronation.
[NAGI]
Are you talking about Schwartz?
[AOI]
Your Highness.
[SAKOMIZU]
Well...
It's scary, isn't it?
To think that with a
single black letter,
an ordinary person will
lose control of their body
and turn into a
ruthless destroyer.
Yup, it's heavy stuff.
But don't worry,
I just saw Mashiro in the
throne room a few minutes ago.
Though she might be a
little angry right now.
[SAKOMIZU, AOI]
Huh?
[ARIKA]
Hey, listen...
[MASHIRO]
What is it?
[ARIKA]
Where in the world are we?
[MASHIRO]
How should I know?
[ARIKA] Well, why not?
It's your castle, isn't it?
[MASHIRO] This castle has
almost 300 years of history,
whereas I am only 14.
[ARIKA]
What's that got to do with it?
Well, anyway, there
isn't much to this place.
[MASHIRO] You have no idea
about anything, do you?
[ARIKA]
Huh?
[MASHIRO]
They say that in the days
of the War of the Twelve Kings,
many tragic battles were fought,
all due to the abundance
of machinery like this.
Really?
[MASHIRO]
Really. Wait, what?!
You don't even know
something basic like that?
That's why I'm
studying about it now!
[MASHIRO] The person who
finally ended the war
was the very first Otome,
the holder of the
Pure White Diamond.
She's the predecessor
for all you Otome.
[ARIKA]
Ah.
I'm actually named
after her gemstone.
"Mashiro" means pure white.
My father and mother
gave me that name.
[ARIKA]
Oh.
To tell the truth,
I'm a little jealous.
As far back as I can remember,
my father and mother
weren't around,
and I never knew who they were.
And though I really
like the name Arika,
I don't know if it's the
name my parents gave me.
But hey, no matter what,
I'm still me. Arika Yumemiya.
And, um... Mashiro, you're
still Mashiro. So, uh...
What I mean is...
You're kidding me.
Please don't tell me
that you, of all people,
are trying to cheer
me up right now.
[ARIKA] Why would I do
a thing like that?
Okay then.
Because if I did receive
sympathy from you,
then I'd know I hit
my lowest point.
[ARIKA]
What do you mean by that?!
[MIKOTO meows]
[MASHIRO]
Mikoto, don't go too far ahead.
[MIKOTO meows]
[MASHIRO]
Mikoto!
[ARIKA]
Where are you?
[BOTH gasp]
[ARIKA]
What is this place?
[MASHIRO] Something like this
was beneath the castle?
Hey, wait!
[ARIKA] Relax! I'm just
gonna take a closer look.
What is this thing?
Stop!
[ARIKA]
Wow!
What is it?
[MASHIRO] Hmm... It looks
like some sort of organ.
[MASHIRO, ARIKA scream]
[ALL scream]
[WORKERS screaming]
What the hell's that?!
[STUDENTS screaming]
[NATSUKI]
Huh? What?
[MASHIRO]
What just happened?
[ARIKA]
Huh?
Ah!
Oh no!
What am I gonna do about this?!
[VOICE]
Not enough.
[screams]
[ARIKA gasps]
[ARIKA]
Who...? What are you?
[VOICE] Not enough.
This is still not enough.
[ARIKA]
What do you mean, "not enough"?
[VOICE] If you wish to utilize
the power of this Harmonium,
you must bring the song,
the player, and the protector.
Wait a minute!
Hey!
[MASHIRO]
Run! Or we'll be trapped inside!
[ARIKA]
What?!
Hey, wait for me!
[MASHIRO]
Why should I?
[MAN A]
I found it.
At last, all our wishes
will be granted.
[ARIKA]
Hey, you in there!
Open up right now! What about
my Gemstone?! Come out!
Bring the song, the player,
and the protector...
[MIKOTO meows]
[MIKOTO hissing]
[MASHIRO] Mikoto! Where the heck
have you been all this time?
[MASHIRO screams]
What's that?
Over there!
[MASHIRO screams]
It's a big ugly monster!
Arika, hurry up
and do something!
I still have a lot of things
I wanna do before I die!
Yeah? Well so do I! Huh?
I still have...
...lots of dreams!
Huh?
These things are...
[gasps]
[ARIKA]
...Blue Gemstones.
Don't tell me...
Uh-oh, look out!
[gasps]
[ARIKA]
I knew it!
What are you doing?
[ARIKA]
Mashiro, give me your left hand!
My left hand? Huh?
[ARIKA]
Good.
[MASHIRO]
Wh-What is this?
Uh, let's see, we gotta...
Oh right!
The contract and authorization!
Huh? Why should I?!
[ARIKA]
Please!
You have to believe in me!
Arika Yumemiya.
Do you solemnly swear to
accept me as your master?
[ARIKA]
Mh-hm.
I guess so!
What do you mean,
"I guess so"?
Then listen to me, Arika.
In my name, I hereby
release your powers.
Yes, Master!
'Kay.
Materialize!
[yelling]
That was incredible.
Yeah! Just like I
thought it would be!
[SLAVE A roars]
All right. Here I go!
Yeah!
[yelping]
What the heck do you
think you're doing?
[chuckles]
Sorry, my mistake.
But look, I can fly!
This is awesome!
Let's try again. Here I go!
Nice going, Arika!
All right! Ah!
[screams]
[MIKOTO meows]
[NATSUKI]
If you become a Meister Otome,
that is, become a full-fledged
Otome who serves a master,
you must remain by
your master's side
and share your life force
with theirs through your Gem.
Mother, if you can hear me,
please lend me your power!
[yelling]
[yells]
[ARIKA]
Let's go!
[gasps]
[chuckles]
[MIKOTO meows]
[ARIKA, MASHIRO]
All right!
[MIKOTO meows]
Hey, where'd that depressed
guy wander off to?
[WORKER D]
I dunno.
And that little girl still
hasn't come back either.
What's with these kids nowadays?
[SAKOMIZU]
It's no good.
We still can't find her.
We have no choice but
to tell Garderobe--
[ARIKA, MASHIRO screaming]
[ARIKA]
Hey, would you get off me?!
[MASHIRO]
I can't help it!
[AOI]
Miss Mashiro!
[SERGEY]
Antsy!
[BOTH]
Huh?
[MASHIRO]
Listen up, Arika!
What happened today
is a secret, okay?
I know that!
I can't let anyone know
I have a contract with you!
[MASHIRO]
You're the one who suggested it!
At any rate, you're the
one who's responsible
for finding a way to
cancel the contract.
You don't have to tell me!
[BOTH giggle]
[MASHIRO]
Drive.
Right!
Back to work! Sorry, boss!
[NAGI]
Aw, my marriage proposal failed!
[SERGEY] It's important
to set the proper mood.
Hug her tightly,
and then like this...
[MASHIRO] Ah! What are you
two doing?! You're both men!
Perverts! Perverts!
[SERGEY]
No! This is just practice!
[NAGI] Guess it's too
late now. Please, continue.
[SERGEY]
What?