[NATSUKI] A weapon that's
designed to destroy planets?
Yes.
Meister Nao Zhang forwarded
the data from the ruins to us
along with her request
to materialize.
From that, we were
able to identify it
as an ancient weapon
called Yuna.
[GAL] It's been programmed
to gain power over time
and become
exponentially stronger.
At the same time,
it deploys Sub-Unit Monsters
known as Childs
in order to attack.
[IRINA]
After a while,
it evolves into the strongest
being on the planet and then...
...it destroys everything.
[roars]
Do you know why it woke up now?
This is only a guess,
but I believe that due to
its incredible strength,
its creator was
unable to control it
and shot it into space.
At this rate, the world will...
[NAGI] It'll be the end...
of everything.
How could this happen, Nina?
I only need Father!
I don't need anyone else!
[screams]
[MIKOTO] The cat food looks
delicious too, Big Brother.
[gasps]
I tried making it using
ingredients I could get
from the sea around us.
Would you mind giving it a try?
You're pretty creative
considering our situation.
[RIBBON] We could add these to
the Cat God Ramen Noodles menu!
Oh, hey there!
Good morning, Nina!
I thought you'd never get up!
Queen Mashiro?
[CAPTAIN A] This is Vergilius
of Remus. We're moving out!
[CAPTAIN B] Wait a minute,
we were gonna move out first!
[CAPTAIN A]
Don't talk back to us, Romulus!
[CONTROLLER A]
Everyone, please!
You must wait for
your turn to depart!
[LAULA]
We can't sit here waiting!
[CARLA]
That's right!
[NATSUKI]
We'll be returning to Wind.
What are you planning
to do, Arika?
I'm gonna continue searching
for Mashiro and the others
for as long as I can.
Right now, I can't use
my Otome powers anyway.
Understood.
Garderobe will handle matters
within the city. All right?
Thank you very much,
Headmistress.
[GAL]
Hey, Arika!
[ARIKA]
Gal!
[GAL] Good news from our leader!
Come on, let's ride!
[NAGI]
All right then.
[chuckles]
Hey, you guards!
Bring me a phone!
I need to talk with
the Headmistress
of Garderobe right away!
[MIDORI] A legend from long ago
has led me to this point.
The Black Valley is on the
other side of that storm.
We can't pass even
with Gakutenou.
It almost feels like
a fading dream.
[ARIKA]
Leader!
[MIDORI]
Hm?
[ARIKA]
Leader!
Is it true?
I heard that you got
a message from Mashiro!
I did. This is the letter.
"I am trapped on an island
surrounded by a giant storm.
You must hurry and come get me."
Mashiro...
[MAI]
Hmm... So that's what happened.
[NINA]
Yes.
Oh, um, excuse me. I didn't
mean to eat everything...
You must've been
really starving, huh?
By the way, Nina, did Arika...
did she say anything to you?
I'm sorry to
disappoint you, but...
...I'm afraid I didn't get
the chance to see Arika.
[MASHIRO]
Oh.
Just what does Arika think
she's doing, anyway?
She doesn't understand
my hardships.
It's like she's not maturing
except for in the
size of her breasts.
Aw, Mashiro,
you're really lonely
without Arika here, aren't you?
[RIBBON]
Right!
Uh! That's not true!
Now that I come to
think of it, Nina,
You should've been my Otome
right from the start!
No... I don't think so.
[MASHIRO gasps]
[MASHIRO] Never mind,
I'm going for a walk.
[MAI, RIBBON laugh]
Arika, we're heading back
to protect the village.
Will you be able to keep
going on your own?
Don't worry, I'll be fine!
Thank you so much for your help!
[GAL] Arika, you've got
a good game face on.
Now go get 'em!
Thank you, Professor Gal!
[ARIKA]
I'm on my way, Mashiro.
Ugh. But how?
I mean, I don't even know
if I can swim very far...
[bell chiming]
[ARIKA]
Huh?
What is that?
[gasps]
Ah!
[RIBBON]
Bam, bam!
May I have some, please?
[NINA] Black Valley really
is a mysterious place.
[RIBBON] The Cat Goddess
showed me how to do that.
[RIBBON]
Miss Nina?
Does Queen Mashiro not
like Miss Arika anymore?
[NINA]
Huh?
Of course not. Not a chance.
Despite what it might look like,
those two get along really well.
[RIBBON]
Really?!
[NINA] Yes. That's why they
end up fighting all the time.
They're more like
childhood friends
than a queen and her Otome.
[RIBBON]
Ohh.
But I really envy Otomes.
All of them are beautiful
and strong! They're so cool!
It's not really what you think.
Obtaining that sort of power can
actually be a frightening thing.
If you take one wrong step,
you might end up
making a major mistake
that can never be fixed again.
[RIBBON] Oh, I get it!
So it's the same as this, then?
But that's--!
You have one too?
[rumbling]
[gasps]
What's going on?!
[RIBBON whimpers]
[RIBBON]
The mountain!
[MAI]
Hm?
The mountain's crying?
Huh?
It's coming...
The dragon that broke through
from the other world...
This is bad! Where are
Mashiro and Nina?
[NATSUKI] Give me a status
report on all nations!
[IRINA] Delta Otome Unit
in Aries: Standing by.
Meister Laula and Meister Carla
are standing by in Lutesia
at the border between
Romulus and Remus.
Meister Anh in Annam:
Standing by.
Florince and Cardair are both
ready to attack as well.
[NATSUKI] And the countries
without Meisters?
[IRINA]
Meister Sara in Windbloom
and Meister Mahya in Artai
have both moved into position
for the attack.
The Surrogate System
is also ready.
We can take action at any time.
[NATSUKI]
All right.
There is a high probability
that the Childs will hatch
if we attack.
[YUKINO]
That's true.
But even if we wait,
they will eventually hatch.
We should take the initiative.
That's the consensus from
the representatives.
Yes, very well.
May the Predecessor's
grace be upon us.
Give word to begin the attack.
Certify Sara and
Mahya's contracts.
Yes, ma'am. Activating
the Surrogate System.
I need your
authorization, Mikoto!
Materialize!
Evacuate to the mountain!
But Her Majesty is
still out there!
I know that!
[IRINA]
It doesn't look like we're able
to inflict any kind of
critical damage on them.
I just hope that we can defeat
them before they hatch.
Annoying sprouts, aren't they?
[GAL]
Sorry I'm late!
What is that?
It's the Predecessor Fumi?!
[YOHKO] Strong certification
wave confirmed!
[IRINA]
Lady Fumi is reacting!
[GAL]
Our server is being hacked!
Link confirmed between
Lady Fumi and the Childs!
It's constantly supplying them
with high level
materializing energy!
So that's it. That's
how it's doing this!
Professor! Sever the
connection immediately!
[GAL]
I can't do it!
The administrator's taken
control of the network!
[YOHKO]
Look!
The Childs in each
of the countries
all of them have
begun to hatch!
No! Mai!
[MASHIRO screams]
[screams]
Arika!
[ARIKA]
Mashiro!
Hang on, Mashiro!
Arika!
I'm almost there!
Mashiro, the authorization!
I know!
The power of the Blue
Sky hasn't returned!
[CARLA yells]
Damn it! It's like there's
no end to this fight!
[IRINA] It's just like
what happened in Aries!
The Childs are
restoring themselves.
Damn it! There's gotta be
a way to stop them, but what?
Ugh! What is it?
You bastard.
What did you say?
I said there's a way
to stop those Childs.
You're in a bit
of trouble, right?
And I have an idea
how to save you.
Do you want to hear it?
But of course under
one condition.
[growls]
[NATSUKI]
Just hurry up and tell me!
[ARIKA]
No!
[screams]
[RIBBON]
I'm scared!
[MIKOTO meowing]
[RIBBON]
Your Majesty!
[NINA]
Wait! Where are you going?
[RIBBON]
I'm gonna fight too!
No, you mustn't!
[RIBBON] But I have to!
It's the only thing I can do!
I like Queen Mashiro
and Miss Arika a lot!
And I also like Miss Nina,
and Meister Mai,
and the Cat Goddess,
and the cat,
and the dolphin too!
That's why I wanna protect them!
Because all of them
are my friends!
[gasps]
[RIBBON]
Miss Nina?
You can put that thing away.
I am going to fight instead.
[RIBBON]
Huh?
Ah! Then Miss Nina, you're a--!
I will never make the
same mistake again.
I'm going to give you a future.
Let's go!
A contract? You and me?
It's the Neptune Emerald.
Please make me your Otome,
even if it is just this once.
But...
[NINA] I've regretted
the mistakes I made.
And I became afraid of
the power of the Otome.
No, actually, the idea
of power itself.
But I want to
protect my friends.
So please...
You mean you're willing
to trust me as your master?
I am.
You were the one who
was able to stop
both Grand Duke Nagi and myself.
I trust you and Arika.
I know we all think the same.
I understand.
Nina Wang. Hear me, my Otome
of the Neptune Emerald.
In my name, I hereby
release your powers!
Stay here and be a
good girl, all right?
Just leave the fighting
to us Otomes.
Materialize!
[RIBBON]
Wow! So cool!
I'm counting on you, Nina!
[yells]
Wait, but that's--!
It's Nina...
[NINA] Your defense is
full of holes as always.
I can't bear to watch it,
so I may as well help you out.
It's really you?
[ARIKA]
Nina!
Arika!
Mashiro!
[MASHIRO]
Arika!
What happened to the
Blue Sky's power?
[ARIKA]
It's gone...
Arika, I want you to slap me.
[ARIKA]
Huh?
Okay, but only if you
do the same to me too!
Hit me again the next time
I make a mistake like that.
Yeah, same goes for me too.
Don't hold back, okay?
You betcha!
[RIBBON]
Good luck!
Yep! You can just
leave it to me!
Let's do it, Arika!
Give my Otome the
power of the Blue Sky!
[RIBBON]
Power!
Blue Sky!
[IRINA] We've found the
coordinates of Cat God Mountain!
We're detecting
high-level materialization
from Gems and Yuna!
What's that?
Confirming it now.
The Fire Stirring Ruby, Meister
Mai, is in combat with a Child.
I also detect Arika,
the Blue Sky Sapphire Zwei.
And the other is...
It's the lost Gem!
The Neptune Emerald.
[NATSUKI]
A lost Gem? Who's the Otome?
It-It's Nina!
Nina?
[gasps]
[NATSUKI]
Nina Wang?
[yells]
Got her!
No way!
[NINA growls]
[NATSUKI] Arika, Nina,
Mai, can you hear me?
Natsuki?
[NATSUKI] We've been able to
pick up on your signal again.
Listen, we're about to
commence a new operation
in order to counterattack.
I want everyone to
listen in on this.
The Childs and Yuna are able
to resurrect themselves
because they've absorbed
the Predecessor.
In a moment, we'll be using
the last core cylinder
of the Surrogate System
in order to sever
the connection.
However, we only
have 120 seconds.
All the Childs and Yuna
need to be defeated
within that timeframe.
Can you do it?
No, you have to do it.
It's the only hope of
protecting this planet
and the world's future.
I never knew you were this big
of a gambler, Headmistress.
Now, about releasing me
from this place... Uh?
Hello?
Hey, wait a minute!
Let's do this. Activate
the Surrogate System.
Connect it to the
Valkyrie Circuit!
[GAL]
Starting contact!
[IRINA] Activating certification
jamming system.
Begin countdown.
Run now!
[screams]
[RIBBON]
Your Majesty!
No! Mashiro!
Arika!
Now what are we gonna do?
[MASHIRO] Don't worry about me!
Do what you have to do, Arika!
[ARIKA gasps]
Mashiro!
[MASHIRO]
You and I aren't the same,
but that's exactly why
we can come together
when it really counts.
And when that happens,
we have to keep going
without hesitation!
Right, Arika?
You're my Otome!
Of course, Master.
You can't be thinking
of attacking!
[ARIKA]
Come on, let's do it, Nina!
If anyone can do it,
we certainly can!
You and Mashiro... it's like
you were made for each other.
A queen and her Otome.
[IRINA]
Ten more seconds!
[yells]
Arika...
Damn you!
[MAI]
Huh?
System down!
What about Yuna?
Has it been defeated?
Yes, it has!
And all the Childs around
the world are vanishing too!
[GAL]
Looks like it's all clear.
[banging]
You did well to get
through this crisis.
Though it took a little while.
[WOMAN A] The number you have
dialed is no longer in service.
[gasps]
Aw, you can't do
this to me, Natsuki!
[RIBBON]
Meister Mai!
Welcome back!
Thanks for all your
hard work, everyone!
I've got a gift for you.
[RIBBON]
It's a new cat!
It took me quite a lot of
effort to catch him, you know.
[MIKOTO]
He's called Kagutsuchi.
Oh, you're awake at last!
Mai... I'm really hungry.
Honestly...
By the way, where's Mashiro?
I think...
[MASHIRO]
Look at that view...
All the stars...
and the sun is rising!
[ARIKA]
This is our world!
It's the planet that we've all
worked so hard to protect.
Look! We can see
it now, Mashiro!
Down there! It's Windbloom!
[MASHIRO] It looks so small,
but... it's so beautiful...
I wanted to bring you up here
so you could see
it for yourself!
So you've been seeing
the world we live in
from a place like this?
[ARIKA]
Yup!
Well it's no wonder you never
care about the small stuff.
Hey, what's that
supposed to mean?
Arika,I wanna go
see even more!
More of this planet. More of
this world we all live in!
So, let's have a race
toward that sun!
Yes, Master!
I'm gonna be an Otome!
You can bet on that!