[MAN A]
Hang in there, Father.
[GIRL A] Mama. I'm so cold...
What happened to our home?
Please, I beg you,
give my child some milk!
[SOLDIER A]
Hey, you!
[gasps]
[MIMI]
What do you want?
[SOLDIER A] Well, little girl,
we're looking for Queen Mashiro.
She's gone missing.
Have you seen her around?
How could I've seen her before?
And who cares anyway?
What I wanna know is, why
did we hafta get kicked out?
I thought the military was
supposed to protect us citizens.
Sorry, kid, but these orders
are coming from above
and we gotta follow 'em.
Besides, people like you
hardly qualify as citizens.
You have no homes or jobs,
you don't pay taxes,
or do anything productive.
You just live in slums.
[MAN B]
It's not like we had a choice!
[SOLDIER A, SOLDIER B]
Huh?
[SOLDIER A]
Let's go.
Damn... just like that, the
military has switched sides,
and now they're all
working for Artai.
[MAN B] Why do we have
to be treated like this?
[MASHIRO] How did I end up
in this terrible situation?
Why is this happening to me?
Somebody, help me...
[MASHIRO] Aoi... Sakomizu...
Mikoto... Arika...
I'm here... Right here...
[gasps]
[groans]
Where am I?
So, you're finally awake.
Jeez, some Headmistress you are.
Just how long were
you gonna sleep?
[NATSUKI]
Huh?
[gasps]
Tell me, what happened
to Wind City?
And Garderobe, and
Arika, and the others?!
[grunts]
Hands.
[NATSUKI]
Hm?
I'm one of the Five Pillars now,
so I'm supposed
to be equal rank.
Do you think this sort
of thing is allowed?
So?
The truth is...
[NATSUKI]
Mh-hm.
...I haven't got a clue!
[growls]
Damn it, Nao!
[screams]
You should eat up. It tastes
pretty good actually.
But... But it's a...
What's this?
Don't tell me this
kind of cuisine
doesn't suit the palate
of the Headmistress.
Does that lecture about "do
whatever it takes to survive"
only apply in the classroom?
Give me that thing!
[NATSUKI]
Three days?!
Yep. That's how long it's
been since the brawl.
Were you the one who rescued me?
That's right.
You should thank me.
Hey, in case it
slipped your mind,
I was the one who saved her.
Don't take credit for
something you didn't do.
Who's he? He's rather
suspicious looking.
Oh, this is my informant.
Actually, you could say
he's an old friend of mine.
If you want to know what
happened in the city,
I can certainly tell you.
But... it's gonna cost you.
If you like,
you can pay me later.
You're good for it, right?
Well, I suppose I
don't have a choice.
[YAMADA]
Grand Duke Nagi declared himself
the liberator of this
city after his army
forced out the Schwartz
and their Slaves.
He took over the
Queen's position
and seized the
military for himself.
He's now occupying Fuka Palace
and has control of the nation.
Quite an ingenious tactic.
The timing for this
was all too perfect.
The only explanation is that it
was all part of a master plan.
Nao, are you sure you
weren't warned about this?
Hey, if I had known about it,
I would've run away long before
all the commotion started.
[NATSUKI groans]
You really are a piece of work.
Despite the number
of new refugees,
it seems the majority
of the citizens
have accepted the change
in leadership favorably.
Refugees?
[YAMADA] They started
to get rid of the people
living in the slums
under the guise of
maintaining public peace.
It's the oldest trick in
the books, but it works.
Establishing a policy
of persecution
raises the standards for
the remaining citizens.
Damn that Nagi!
What about Garderobe?
Is the school also
under his control?
[YAMADA]
Yes,
but since they've tightened
security around the campus,
it's hard to know
what's going on.
Shizuru...
What about the other nations?
No reaction.
For now, I expect they'll
sit back and remain neutral.
[HARUKA] That stupid little
runt Nagi has some nerve!
There's no way I'm gonna
let him get away with this!
Haruka, stop!
Artai did not break
any international laws
with their actions.
If we try to do
something about it now,
it would be seen as an invasion.
Out of my way, Yukino.
The school I once came
from is in a dark time.
My mind's made up. I'm going.
And it doesn't matter
what you say!
You're going, no matter what?
Well then, I have no choice.
I'm really sorry, Haruka.
[ARGOS] That boy from Artai,
he's really done it this time.
Windbloom would be bad enough,
but he also has his
hands on Garderobe.
We no longer have the
luxury of staying back
and observing from a distance.
[NATSUKI]
Considering what's happened,
it's good news that
the Queen and Arika
haven't fallen under
Nagi's control.
[NATSUKI]
Huh?
You've been saying some
very interesting things.
Tell me, what's happened
to Arika Yumemiya?
[NAO yelps]
I suggest you stop.
Without their Robes,
Otomes do not stand a chance
against me in combat.
Who-Who are you?
Who I am is not the
important issue here.
Again, what happened to Arika?
Tell me, Ice Silver Crystal.
[ARIKA yells]
[NINA yells]
[NATSUKI] A tremendous amount
of power was unleashed
when the two
Gemstones collided.
[MIYU] So the Ultimate Black
Diamond has once again
made an appearance on
the stage of history.
[YAMADA]
I've heard that Grand Duke Nagi
has sent out a
large search party,
but so far they've not been able
to locate the Queen or the girl.
So there you have it.
We don't know where Arika might
be any more than you do.
After an incident like this, I
just hope that she's all right.
[NAO]
Oh, I'm sure she is.
And I bet the Queen is too.
Those types of people
are very resilient.
Besides, it seems Nina was
doing fine afterwards.
[MIYU]
Nina...
Is that the name of the Otome
who now wields the
Ultimate Black Diamond?
[NATSUKI]
Yes.
[ERSTIN]
No!
[NATSUKI]
She must be miserable now
because of what
happened to Erstin...
...your friend...
that's why... I...
[NATSUKI]
This is my fault.
Schwartz was able to
infiltrate the Academy
without me knowing.
If only I'd been more careful,
I could've stopped all
of this from happening.
[knocking]
[NINA]
It's me, Father.
Come in.
Nina... I'm so...
Father, you mustn't get up yet.
You're pushing
yourself too hard.
Your wounds still
haven't fully healed.
You haven't touched
a bite of your food!
Hey, you're only hurting
yourself if you don't eat!
Uh, right...
Is the food not to your liking?
I can always go and make
something else for you.
No... It's... okay...
Well then how about some fruit?
Wait, I know! Grapes are
in season right now.
They've always been your
favorite, right, Father?
The stores outside
are back in business.
I'll go and find some for you.
[SERGEY]
Nina- chan !
I'm so sorry.
This is all my fault.
[NINA]
Don't apologize to me!
Please, Father. If you
apologize to me, I...
[NINA crying]
[SERGEY]
Damn it!
This is it?
Yes.
The Harmonium.
At last, the wondrous science
that we've been
chasing for so long.
[NAGI]
This thing, huh?
So is it operational?
It's been two centuries
since it was last used.
Now it won't even budge an
inch, no matter what we try.
We haven't been able
to crack the seal
on the mausoleum either.
It looks like we need to
follow proper procedures
in order to open them.
[NAGI]
Well, that is a problem.
The song, the player,
and the protector, right?
[SMITH] That's what it
says in our Sacred Book.
Fortunately, as far
as the song goes,
we already have the lyrics
for the first two verses,
thanks to the work
of Saint Erstin.
And the third verse
should be with Mashiro?
Well, she was raised to be
the Queen of this nation.
So, she should know it.
I see. So the "song" is Mashiro.
And if Sergey is right about
the real Princess thing,
the player would be Arika.
We'll definitely
need to find her.
[SMITH]
Yes.
[MAN D]
Damn...
The Aries will
take us in, right?
They won't turn us
away, will they?
[MAN E]
This is all the Queen's fault.
Blame her for us
ending up like this.
[MAN F] But wasn't it that
Nagi guy who kicked us out?
[MAN E]
Yeah, but I was unemployed
because of that Queen.
And all the while,
those bribe-taking politicians
and construction contractors
were getting rich.
And then we end up
with that castle.
Pathetic.
Restart the construction
from scratch.
We shall rebuild this castle
into something completely new.
[TAKUMI]
I can't ignore the fact
that the Queen's having these
big birthday celebrations
and having her castle rebuilt
when she should
really be dealing
with a lot more
important issues.
For example, think about
the place where you woke up.
[MASHIRO]
If they don't have bread,
well then, they can
always eat candy!
[TAKUMI] I can see that
you're very fortunate.
[MASHIRO] What's wrong with me
doing things the way I like?
I'm the Queen.
[MAN G]
I'll bet the rumors were true.
She was probably an
imposter after all.
[WOMAN A]
I've had it with that Princess.
Both the King and Queen were
decent, honorable people,
but she's nothing like them!
[WOMAN B]
You're right.
Maybe the rumor that's going
around really is true.
But I'm still...
This girl is the real Princess!
She is the real
daughter of the King,
and the true heir of Windbloom!
[gasps]
There's no possible
way that little brat
could ever be the Queen.
I am the real...
I'm so dry, I can't
shed tears...
[MIMI] Hey, you!
You don't look so good.
Are you all right?
Have I seen you
somewhere before?
Uh, I-I think you
must be mistaken.
[MIMI]
Hm.
Well, doesn't matter.
Drink up. Here.
You'll die if you get
left behind, ya know.
Can I... really...?
I'm not gonna force you
if you don't want any.
Hey!
Oh, man, come on! What a waste!
I understand.
In that case, I have no
further questions to ask you.
[NATSUKI]
Why are you looking for Arika?
Although I really don't
expect an answer from you.
That is because it has
nothing to do with you.
Well, can you at least
give us your name?
I am Merciful Intelligential
Yggdrasil Unit.
However, that's
not my only name.
There was once
someone whom I loved.
I gave her everything, and
she gave me the name "Miyu."
Miyu...
[MASHIRO groans]
[MIMI]
Whoa, that looks painful.
I don't think I can
walk another step.
[MIMI]
Hm?
Your skin is really fair.
And your hands and
feet are smooth.
Well, except for the fact
that they're covered
in blisters right now.
Why is that?
Are you some sort of Princess
from another country?
[gasps]
Just kidding!
Why would a Princess be in
an awful place like this?
A Princess would be
eating delicious food
and sleeping on a nice,
soft bed right now.
Really... So unfair.
Mimi... do you also...
...do you also hate the Queen?
[MIMI]
Yeah.
My dad used to be
a baker, y'know.
He had his own bakery,
and even though it
was a small place,
it was filled with lots
of customers every day.
But then some government
officials came to the bakery
and they closed it down.
Something about them
wanting to build a road.
And my dad just lost all his
energy and will to work.
After that, it was
the same old story.
Drinking, debt, gambling...
the whole works.
In the end, he died a pitiful
death by the side of that road.
Every time I look at the castle,
I always think the same thing.
The Queen has never done
a thing for any of us.
She never listens, and
doesn't watch over us either.
And that's because, from
way up there in her castle,
she can't even see us.
There's no way she
could understand
what we're going through.
So that's why I decided not
to look up at the Queen either.
I refuse to look up at her!
Why should I look at someone
who does stuff like that
stupid birthday party?
That's why I hate the Queen!
Ugh! I hate her!
Mimi...
[stomach growls]
[MIMI]
Huh?
Wait here a minute.
Up until now, was I...?
[MIMI]
Here.
[MASHIRO]
You can have it.
It's really... good...
Huh? It's not really that good.
Actually, it tastes awful.
The guy warned me
about the taste.
He said it's 'cause
we're low on salt.
No... it's delicious.
It's the first
time in my life...
...I ever realized...
food can be so good.
Hey, come on! Don't start
crying! It's just some stew!
Jeez, what kind of life
did you have before?
Huh?
Is it true?
Yeah, it is.
We met up with another
group a little while ago.
It seems she managed
to join in with them.
Hey, everyone, come on!
We just caught someone
who worked in the castle!
One of the Queen's maids!
[gasps]
[AOI screams]
[WOMAN B] This woman...
I've seen her before!
[MAN K] She's Queen
Mashiro's personal aide!
[MAN L]
While we were starving,
she was living the
life of luxury!
[MAN M] Damn her. She tried to
escape by hiding among us!
[MASHIRO]
Aoi!
[MAN N] This is all
because of you people!
Give me back my wife!
My home! My job!
[MAN E] It's because you
let that stupid Queen
do whatever she wanted!
[MASHIRO]
Aoi!
[MAN P]
What should we do with her?
[WOMAN C]
Hand her over to Artai!
[MAN Q]
No! That won't erase our anger!
Make her take responsibility!
That's right!
I say we take from her
everything she took from us!
[MASHIRO] I... I never knew
they hated me this much.
[AOI screams]
Well, it serves her right.
But she's just a maid who
happened to work in the castle.
So why...?
She's just the same.
She didn't do anything
to stop the Queen
from messing around
like she did.
And because of that,
we ended up like this.
[MAN E] This is your last
chance to redeem yourself.
Tell us where the Queen is!
We'll let you live if you do.
[MASHIRO]
Aoi...
That's correct! Indeed, I am...
Come on!
Huh? Oh, right.
May I present Mashiro
Blan de Windbloom,
the Crown Princess
and future Queen
over all of Windbloom Kingdom!
I am supposed to be the
Queen of this country!
What's wrong with doing
things the way I like?
That's right.
I should be the one...
My feet... why won't they move?
[MAN E]
Are you sure you don't know?
You'd be a fool to
die for that girl.
I don't know. And even if
I did, I wouldn't tell you.
[gasps]
That's what she gets.
[MAN T]
She deserved it!
Huh, she could've at least cried
or begged for her
life or something.
That wasn't any fun.
Huh? What's wrong with you?
Hey!
[MASHIRO]
I have nothing left.
No nation... No friends...
No honor as a Queen...
[ARIKA]
Let's make it a race.
We'll see if I become
a Meister first,
or you become a Queen first!
How about it?
I already am a Queen!
Then how about... a Queen
who will bring happiness
to everyone in her country?
[MASHIRO]
Arika...
[ARIKA]
Huh?
Hey, Arika? Were you
able to get some water?
[ARIKA]
Yeah! I'll be right there!
Let's go, Mikoto!
[MIKOTO meows]
[MASHIRO]
W... W...
[ARIKA] Worm? Hang in
there, Mashiro! Here!
[MASHIRO] Ah, nice and wet
and slimy-- What the--?!
[ARIKA] Ha! Grandma said you can
find humor almost anywhere.
[MASHIRO] What kinda
person was she, anyway?!
[ARIKA]
Well, she was--
Oh, hey, we're outta time.
[MASHIRO growls]