[howling]
[yelling]
What are you so upset
about, Arika?
I'm trying to write
to my sponsor
but I don't know who it is.
I mean, how do you think
I should address them?
[ERSTIN] The wording and
handwriting looks formal,
so I think the writer's a man.
Hey, what do you think, Nina?
Who knows.
You were asked to write your
sponsor every week, right?
So why don't you figure
it out yourself?
Meanie. Gee, Nina, why
are you always so cold?
[gasps]
Huh?
What? Stop staring!
[ARIKA]
Huh...
[NINA gasps]
Stop that!
[ARIKA]
Heh.
[laughs]
At last, I found
your weak point!
Take this!
Tickle, tickle, tickle...!
[NINA]
No! Stop!
--[laughing]
--[NINA screaming]
This is the first time I've
seen you get like this, Nina!
So cute!
No, stop! Please don't!
[NINA screaming]
[NINA]
Why you!
[ARIKA screams]
[NINA] That's for what
you did to me yesterday!
[ARIKA groans]
Don't ever try that again
unless you want another beating.
You made your point,
but do you think I'm
gonna let end like this?!
[ARIKA, NINA yell]
[BOTH gasp]
Stop this, both of you.
A dance battle must be fought
with grace and charm.
Otomes must not be swayed
by their personal emotions!
[ARIKA]
Hmph.
[growls]
This could be a problem.
Wait, just a moment.
What do you wanna
see me about?
I don't think I've done
anything lately.
Actually, I have a small
favor to ask of you, Nao.
[NAO]
Hm?
[YUKARIKO]
You see...
[ARIKA, NINA]
What?!
[YAYOI]
Room duty?
Yep.
Miss Yukariko said that I'm
being appointed as Nao's helper,
just like Nina, and we both
have to handle room duty.
Wow!
Working for Big Sister Nao,
Pearl Number Four,
I think that's pretty cool!
So what kinds of things do
I have to do for room duty?
Let's see.
Well, you have to clean her
room, and make lunch for her.
Basically, you hafta
do her daily chores.
In return, she'll do things
like be your sparring partner,
or help you study.
Yeah, but you have to follow any
order the Big Sister gives you.
Even if it's this, or that,
you're not allowed
to refuse her!
It sounds like a pain.
[TOMOE]
It's probably an attempt
to bring you and Nina
closer together.
[IRINA] Right, especially after
that big fight earlier today.
Well, I let things
get outta hand.
This all started when
I found Nina's weak point.
Weak point?
Now I'm interested!
You wanna know? Well...
[IRINA]
Hmm...
Really?
[gasps]
Irina! No!
Wow! Sexy!
Isn't she?
[NINA]
Arika!
[NINA growling]
N-N-Nina!
Arika!
[ARIKA screams]
[SHIHO]
My goodness!
How surprising!
Who would've known Nina
could be so ticklish?
It was totally adorable!
Oh?
It makes me wonder if they
have any other weaknesses,
either Nina, or Arika.
Oh, Miya, do you know
if they have any?
[MIYA]
Huh?
I... Well, I...
I... don't know much about...
Nina... I'm afraid.
I know! Arika doesn't
know how to swim!
Really?!
Yeah!
We were talking about our
swimming classes tomorrow.
You've never swam before?
Nope! So I'm really
looking forward to it!
And that's what she said!
I see...
[SHIHO]
Seven maki-maki's for Nina Wang.
Three maki-maki's
for Arika Yumemiya.
[chuckles]
You defied me, a member of
the prosperous clan of Cardair,
so you must be punished
by the spinning maki-maki!
Red maki-maki, blue maki-maki,
yellow maki-maki, red maki-maki,
blue maki-maki,
yellow maki-maki,
maki-maki, maki-maki,
spin, spin, maki-maki,
maki-maki, maki-maki!
[screams]
[SHIHO cackles]
[SHIHO]
Spiral! Spiral!
[ARIKA gasps]
[ARIKA] We swim here?
It's a big bathtub!
Somethin' like that.
Are you sure you're ready?
Of course I am!
Or I would like to say that.
But a weird person's watching!
Who are you calling weird?
After hearing that
you can't swim,
I simply had to come and watch.
You're wrong! This is
just my first time!
So you can't swim then.
I can swim! I'm sure!
And what's with that weird
bathing suit you're wearing?
Ugh! You're calling
me weird again!
This swimsuit was passed down
through generations
of the royal family!
[grunts]
[ARIKA] Doesn't matter!
What's weird is weird!
[MASHIRO]
You ignorant commoner!
[ERSTIN chuckles]
It's nice. They're almost
like old friends.
They're just noisy.
All right, everybody, line up.
Ah, Arika. As for you...
Yes?
[YUKARIKO]
Since it's your first time,
you'll begin by sinking
your face into the water
and opening your eyes.
No way!
Do the best that you can.
I'll check on your
progress later.
Huh?
[MASHIRO clears throat]
[ARIKA] This is just like
washing my face!
It'll be easy!
Huh?
[grunts]
[ARIKA]
Huh...?
Aww!
[MASHIRO clears throat]
[ARIKA grunting]
[splash]
[MASHIRO laughing]
[MASHIRO]
I'll never get tired
of watching you make
a fool of yourself!
[IRINA]
Oh boy, what's she up to now?
I'm a kinda surprised.
It's unusual to see
Arika get like that.
[NINA sighs]
[NINA]
Those two are just plain idiots.
[ERSTIN gasps]
[IRINA]
Huh?
What's wrong?
Uh, I think
there's something...
[ERSTIN gasps]
Nina? I--
Huh?
You really shouldn't
do that, Nina.
After all, we're
both girls, right?
Not that I'm not saying
it wouldn't be nice...
Huh?
[LILIE yelps]
[PATRICIA gasps]
[TOMOE gasps]
Uhh... That's odd.
[YUKARIKO] Everyone,
please get out of the water
and form lines by
the side of the pool.
I will be timing each of you.
[whistle blows]
Wow, Nina's actually
pretty good at this!
Huh, must be nice.
[chuckles]
Yeah, here's my chance to
teach you a lesson, Nina Wang.
[gasps]
[screams]
[SHIHO] Maki-maki, maki-maki,
maki-maki, maki-maki,
maki-maki, maki-maki...
[moaning]
[NINA]
No!
Oh, Nina.
[SHIHO] Maki-maki, maki-maki,
maki-maki, maki-maki,
maki-maki, maki-maki.
[moaning]
Nina!
Oh no!
[ARIKA]
Nina!
Arika?
[ARIKA screams]
[groans]
How are you feeling?
Father...
Thank goodness!
I don't know what
I would've done
if something had
happened to you.
Miss Yukariko was so
worried about you,
she contacted Major Wang
and told him to come here.
I, uh...
[SERGEY]
It's not like you to drown.
And don't forget
to say thank you
to Erstin and Antsy here.
These two were the
ones who saved you.
You two did?
Well, I jumped in, but I nearly
ended up drowning with you.
But hey! At least now I can
put my face in the water!
Then...
[YUKARIKO]
Yes.
It was Erstin who
performed CPR on you.
CPR?
All my thanks,
and sorry to cause you all
this trouble, Miss Erstin.
It was no trouble, not at all.
[NINA groans]
[SERGEY]
Huh?
Nina?
[door opens]
Hi, Nina. Get a boo-boo?
[SERGEY]
Huh?
Well, well, if it isn't
dear Major Wang.
Let me welcome you to
the garden of virgins.
Uh! Nao!
Well, it seems you still
haven't had your venom removed.
Look, my marks are
up to standard,
and that's all you care about.
[YOHKO] I know you all came
especially to see her,
but what Nina needs right now
is some rest, don't ya think?
[ARIKA]
Um...
Big Sister Nao, do you know that
Major Wang guy personally?
Yeah. I guess you
could say that.
I'm here 'cause of Artai's
tax money, just like Nina.
What? Are you really?
Yup.
That guy goes around scouting
young women of Artai,
looking for potential Otome
candidates to send here.
Our country is
very cold and poor,
and Grand Duke Nagi doesn't
even have an Otome yet.
They're probably
trying to strengthen
Artai's military power this way.
Military power?
Do you mean for war?
Of course I do.
You can have all the soldiers,
tanks, and battleships you want,
but they're no match against
even a single Meister.
The Otome's power is the
military power of the nation.
That's why Otomes are
so well respected.
[gasps]
You didn't know that?
So then why are you trying
to become an Otome?
Because...
Well, they're beautiful,
cool, and strong!
Ha. Then you and Nina
have something in common.
Who'd've guessed?
She's also a simpleminded moron.
I bet she's feeling really
depressed right about now.
Probably telling herself how
she embarrassed her father.
He might have taken
her under his wing
when she was an orphan,
but there's no need
to try so hard
to please a pathetic
man like him.
That girl is such a fool.
[ARIKA]
How can you say that?
At least she's doing her best!
[NAO]
Hm?
Nina's working as
hard as she can!
You shouldn't be
calling her a "fool"
or any other names like that!
Grandma told me that only a real
fool calls other people fools!
[NAO chuckles]
You really are
interesting, aren't you?
Anyway, you can
leave Nina alone.
Actually, you're probably
better off doing that.
What do you mean by that?
Just that she's very
stubborn, and foolish.
[SHIHO chuckles]
That served you right,
Nina Wang!
Not enough maki-makis
for that Arika girl,
but it still went well.
Now... to destroy... the proof.
[MARIA]
Who's there?
The pool is currently
off-limits. Now go, Shiho Huit.
[SHIHO yelping]
As a member of Trias,
I came here to investigate
the incident!
[MARIA] I appreciate
your good intentions.
However, the investigations
are the job of the school.
No one is permitted here until
the cause has been determined.
But...
[gasping]
[ERSTIN]
Oh! Could this be it?
[IRINA]
Hmm... I wonder...
Irina, what about this one?
None of those have been
transplanted onto this planet.
And besides, do we
even know for sure
there was something in the pool?
I'm not certain, but
Nina insists there was.
[NINA]
Never again...
To have to go through all
that... it's unforgivable.
You know, she looks
kinda possessed.
[IRINA chuckles]
[NINA]
I found it!
[ALL yelp]
This is it. This is the thing.
[IRINA]
Gelle Anguille?
[NINA]
Yes. There's no mistake.
This organism is unique
to this planet,
but is similar to eels
and jellyfish from Earth.
Ninety-eight percent of
its body is made of water,
so they're impossible
to see in water.
However...
[IRINA]
"When it comes into contact
with strong salt concentration,
its body becomes cloudy,
making it easy to see."
Now I get it.
The Headmistress has given
her permission for this,
so I will allow you to proceed.
But if turns out to
be a waste of time,
there will be consequences.
[NINA]
I'm not worried.
[SHIHO]
This could be a problem.
[ARIKA sighs]
[ARIKA]
Well, that's all the salt!
[IRINA]
Yep, we brought it all.
[NINA]
It's too soon to take a break.
It's time to bring those
things to the light!
[ARIKA]
Take this!
[ERSTIN]
And that!
[IRINA laughing]
[ARIKA]
There!
[NINA]
C'mon, show yourselves!
I'm gonna catch you
all in a single net!
[ARIKA]
Hm?
There's nothing here.
[MARIA]
You, girls.
You've wasted all this food.
It's punishment duty
for you. Be prepared.
[ERSTIN, IRINA groan]
[ARIKA]
Hm.
[SHIHO]
Leave them to me, Miss Maria!
I will be sure to
supervise them properly.
Is that so?
Then I'll leave you
in charge of cleanup.
Leave the pool area
as soon as you're done.
There you have it!
You'd better hurry up
with the cleaning!
[IRINA] Oh boy, looks like
Nina's chance to redeem herself
has hit a dead end.
[ERSTIN]
Well, it can't be helped.
My hands are sticky!
[ERSTIN]
Huh?
[IRINA]
Sticky?
[ARIKA]
Mh-hm.
[IRINA groans]
It tastes sweet.
Huh?!
Arika! What did you
do this time?
[ERSTIN]
Sweet.
Ah!
No way!
I went and got all the bags
from the section marked "salt"!
But... it's definitely sugar.
Then...
Arika!
[ARIKA]
Wait a minute!
[SHIHO]
Hm?
[gasps]
"When given sugar,
these organisms will
merge with each other,
absorb the surrounding water,
and grow to enormous size"?!
[ALL scream]
[SHIHO screaming]
[ERSTIN]
Big Sister Shiho!
[yelps]
Erstin!
[whimpering]
Stop!
Go! Run and get one of the
teachers, Irina! Hurry! Now!
Got it!
[ARIKA]
Watch out!
What are you waiting
for?! Save me!
[ERSTIN screams]
What do we do, Nina?
If we could use our Robes,
we could take this thing down!
[SHIHO screams]
Oh no, Big Sister Shiho!
[ERSTIN gasps]
Arika, you run and distract it.
I'm gonna try this
one more time.
Gotcha!
Hey, I'm over here!
[NINA]
I did it!
Nina!
[NINA gasps]
[NINA grunting]
Nina!
[ERSTIN screams]
[gasps]
[IRINA]
Arika!
Hey. Look who that is!
[NAO]
Ugh. Jeez.
You went to all that trouble
just to save someone like her?
Ugh. You girls
really are fools.
[SHIHO grunting]
I can't get out of here!
[grunts]
[NAO] Hi! How's the
maki-maki going?
[NAO chuckles]
[NAO]
This suits you well.
A swirl-headed girl getting
trapped in a swirl herself.
Hurry up and save me, Juliet!
And what are you supposed to say
to someone when you ask a favor?
Would you help me, please?
[NAO]
Huh?
Please help me!
Guess I have to, then.
[screaming]
Big Sister Nao!
That was cool!
WEll, it seems that you
owe me again, Nina.
And you too, Arika.
[SHIHO]
Juliet!
[BOTH]
Hm?
How could you just
dump me here?!
You're a big liar,
you know that?!
Hey, I never said I was
going to help you safely.
You're such an idiot.
[SHIHO]
Juliet! I'm gonna maki-maki you!
[ARIKA]
"Dear, Sir.
Well... I've decided to
start calling you 'Sir.'
Nao, one of the senior
students of the Academy,
told me that that's what
older men like to be called.
Oh, let me tell you
about Nao, my Big Sister.
I've been appointed
to her room duty.
She says she doesn't mind
because she thinks
I'm interesting.
I rely on her, and my
roommates Nina and Ersty,
and so many of my classmates.
I've made lots of friends
at this Academy."
What ugly handwriting.
[ARIKA]
"Classes are difficult,
but I'm enjoying each
and every day very much.
I owe it all to you.
Thank you, Sir."
[NINA]
What was with this episode?
Why did I have to endure that?
[NATSUKI]
I see. So it's you this time.
Then I'll leave the rest to you.
[NINA]
What are you saying?
[NATSUKI]
Don't worry.
Once you get used to it,
you'll find it quite pleasant.
[NINA]
N-No!