[MASHIRO] Wh-What is that?!
I never authorized that design!
Now, let's get started.
Those things...
[PEOPLE screaming]
This is the Schwartz's doing.
Your Majesty, we must
retreat to Garderobe.
Please, authorize us to fight.
Uh... All right.
I, Natsuki Kruger,
Second Pillar and Headmistress
of Garderobe Academy,
hereby make a
request of Our Lady.
This is an emergency.
Please allow all of
your faithful servants
full use of their Robes.
You gotta be kidding.
[NATSUKI] Attention all
students of Garderobe!
Permission granted
to activate Robes.
Your orders are to
protect the guests,
then fall back to the
academy and regroup there.
Mashiro!
[NINA]
Father!
Nina!
You must guard Queen Mashiro.
Huh?
[AOI]
Miss Mashiro... Hang in there.
Thank goodness.
Are you all right?
[MIKOTO meows]
Aoi?
What's going on? What about
the castle? And the city?
I don't know.
We were attacked, and then
there was a loud bang.
It was a close call.
I barely got you
two out of there.
But the others...
Why? Why is this all happening?
[rustling]
Who's there?!
[ARIKA]
Ersty!
[PEOPLE shouting]
Finally, the technology
of Garderobe belongs to us.
We cannot let Schwartz
have their way with it.
Its target was the
port by the desert?
That's right. I want you
to go and check it out.
It's up to you.
I have other things I
need to take care of.
Then let me come with you!
[SERGEY]
Look, you're my daughter.
But the reason I adopted
you and brought you up
was for the sake of His
Highness, Grand Duke Nagi.
And for the future of Artai,
so please, Nina- chan ...
I understand, Father.
[NATSUKI]
amn the Schwartz!
How in the world were they
able to do that to the castle?
It would appear they've managed
to infiltrate much deeper
than we thought possible.
What about Arika?
Has she shown up yet?
Not yet. I'm worried about her.
She could be with the Queen.
Then there still might be hope.
In accordance with Clause C of
the Otome Concealment Treaty,
this Academy will now
take a defensive posture.
I expect everyone to
carry out their duties
and protect this school.
Headmistress, come quickly!
[ALL gasp]
Oh no, things are going
from bad to worse.
[RAD]
Unless you want to die,
I suggest you get
out of our way.
[SMITH] It seems things are
going according to plan.
We should be able to
stall for a bit longer.
It was a long time ago
that our ancestors
created the power of the Otome.
And now, we'll have
it returned to us.
[chuckles]
[SCHWARTZ MEMBER A]
Where is Queen Mashiro hiding?
Spit it out, and
you won't get hurt.
[SCHWARTZ MEMBER B] If anyone
sees her, report it immediately!
No good.
This isn't a safe way to go to
the academy or the castle.
[ARIKA, MASHIRO]
Huh?
Shh!
The Queen...
[growls]
[WOMAN A]
She's here!
She's right over here!
It's Queen Mashiro!
You lousy piece of trash!
Run, everyone!
[SHIZURU] We hear you've been
bullyin' our poor underclassmen.
Aswad, huh?
So your group is also involved
in this. What a surprise.
[MIDORI] We were not the ones
who initiated this attack.
But that's not important.
What matters is
we're here now.
We'll defeat you..
...and take Garderobe
for ourselves!
You certainly have guts.
Let's finish our fight.
Materialize!
I bid you, come out,
Steel Fang!
Gakuten-oh!
[NATSUKI yells]
[MASHIRO] What was with
that woman, anyway?
She should've covered for us!
Instead she sold her
Queen out to the enemy!
Hey, what do you think
we should do now, Ersty?
We don't really have a choice.
We'll have to proceed carefully
so they don't find us.
[MIKOTO grunts]
[hissing]
[ARIKA]
Hm?
[MIKOTO hissing]
Don't anyone move.
Oh, it's you. What do
you think you're doing?
[MASHIRO, ERSTIN, AOI gasp]
[SERGEY]
Come on, let's hurry.
The final setup is
complete, Mister Smith.
Let's begin, shall we?
[NATSUKI]
Huh?
What? This can't be!
Wha--?
Our Robes.
What's going on?
Is this only a game to you?
Why did you just
deactivate your Robe?
[YOHKO]
Stop it, Midori!
[MIDORI]
Hm?
It's Yohko.
[SHIZURU]
Professor, what's goin' on?
The Otome identification
system has malfunctioned.
It's due to a massively
powerful interference
that's forced the entire system
into protective hibernation.
until the interference
disappears
and the Headmistress
restarts the process.
Well, Yohko, we cross
paths once again.
[TOMOE, IRINA scream]
[MIDORI]
Hm?
[gasps]
[SHIZURU]
Huh?
Now it's the Schwartz.
[RAD]
We must retreat.
If we fight with them here,
we risk damaging the mausoleum
and everything inside.
Damn it! Retreat!
Midori! Reito, wait!
[RAD] Don't call me by
that name. My name is Rad.
Rad the cyborg.
Well then, I think I can
leave the rest up to you.
[NINA]
Hm?
[ARIKA]
What in the world happened?
Our Robes disappeared and our
Gemstones have gone funny.
Mine just popped
out really easily.
[SERGEY]
There must be something big
going on at Garderobe Academy.
That's where your
predecessor is,
and she's the source of
power for all the students
as well as the Five Pillars.
Are you sure?
So this might be caused by
the guys from the Schwartz too?
Most likely.
[ARIKA]
What the heck is going on?!
Why are those people
doing all this?!
[SMITH] We're doing this
so that the technology
so conveniently
hidden by Garderobe
can once again be spread
throughout the world.
It's that guy from Schwartz.
You're here? As I recall,
aren't you supposed to be...?
[ARIKA]
Hey you!
I don't know what
you're planning,
but stop getting in our way!
[SERGEY]
Ah!
Huh?
Don't worry, we won't
get in your way.
Just hand over
Queen Mashiro to me,
and the rest of you can
go without any trouble.
Use the Blue Sky Sapphire.
As long as you're a Meister
with your own Master,
it should still work and
let you use your Robe.
Mashiro!
Touch it!
Wh-What?!
I knew it!
Major Wang, do you know
what you just did?!
I command you,
release thy power.
Okay then! Time to get
rid of this weirdo!
Yeah, with pleasure!
Materialize!
The tables have turned now,
you Schwartz creep!
Get outta here
before you get hurt!
Huh... Is that the Blue
Sky Sapphire? What's this?
It looks like you haven't called
forth its full power yet.
All the same, this is
still rather troublesome.
Ah, well...
I really hate to do this,
but it seems I need to call
on someone for back-up.
It's time, Miss Erstin!
[ARIKA]
Uh?
[SMITH] Now is the hour to prove
your loyalty to the Schwartz!
Show your faith in the god
of knowledge and wisdom!
Arika... I...
I'm sorry...
No way... This can't...
This can't be...
It's not true! It's
a joke! Right, Ersty?!
It's no joke.
She is the daughter
of the Ho family,
one of the strongest
supporters of our cause.
She has been trained for
our service since her birth.
Under the contract of darkness,
I fulfill my oath to you.
God of the ancient light,
knowledge, and wisdom,
grant me a loyal servant.
[SCHWARTZ MEMBER E]
Surrender!
Otomes without their Robes
are no match for our power!
Slaves maki-maki, Schwartz
maki-maki, Slaves maki-maki--
That's not gonna work!
"Schwaves" maki-maki,
"Slarz" maki-maki,
maki-maki, maki-maki!
Your tongue's all twisted.
You must remain calm, everyone.
It's during these times
that we must believe
in Our Lady all the more.
[MARIA] Two hundred years
of Garderobe history,
and to think it comes to this...
I'm gonna lure them
away from here.
When I do, you run.
I can't do something like that!
I'm staying here till the end.
Don't say such
childish things, Natsuki!
[NATSUKI]
Huh?
As long as you survive,
Garderobe will survive,
even if the school itself were
to be completely taken over.
You have to run, all right?
I understand.
Now that sounds like
the Natsuki I know.
Don't die!
Ersty, stop!
I'm begging you. Please
hand over Queen Mashiro.
That way, I won't have to--
I can't do that!
I don't understand why
you're doing this, Ersty.
[ERSTIN]
It was decided a long time ago.
By my father, my mother, my
grandparents, even further back!
That's why...
You said it yourself,
didn't you, Arika?
That if everybody
had this technology,
then all of us
would all be happy!
There wouldn't be...
any more...
...any more wars...
I have to!
[gasps]
[screams]
Ersty, what's wrong?
The bond between
a Slave and Lord
is the same as between
an Otome and Master.
If the Slave is hurt, then
the Lord will be hurt as well.
[ARIKA]
No...
[NAGI]
Hey there, Mashiro!
All you have to do is come
along without making a fuss,
and then no one
will have to fight.
Uh! Nagi!
Oh, Mashiro.
Give up already. C'mon!
N-Nina?!
Oh, Erstin... How could you?
Nina- chan .
Father...
Hello there, Sergey. I didn't
expect you to be out here too.
I guess you really
are a hard worker.
Nagi, are you the one
behind all of this?
[chuckles] Yep! Good job.
You figured it out!
See, I have a major problem
with the way that Garderobe
handles things.
Don't you think it's strange?
They claim to maintain peace,
but only by pointing
double-edged swords
called Otomes at each other.
Oh, by the way, you don't have
to worry about your city.
Right now, my army
is in the process
of "liberating" it
from the Slaves.
That's a dirty tactic!
It's called politics.
Now, dear Mashiro, it's time
for you to make a decision.
Will you sit and watch
while these friends of
yours kill each other,
or will you quietly submit
and become my possession?
[MASHIRO growls]
Mashiro, you can't
go along with this!
I don't understand all
this complicated stuff,
but I do know that what
he's doing is wrong!
Oh well, I guess
I have no choice.
You can proceed, Smith.
It's time to finish
this, Miss Erstin!
[gasps]
[ARIKA screams]
I'm so sorry...
Arika... I'm sorry...
What are you waiting
for, Erstin?
That sort of attack isn't
going to kill an Otome!
Please forgive me...
Forgive me.
Arika!
No, Father!
[gasps]
[ARIKA gasps]
[ARIKA]
It's you...
Impossible...
Father was really...?
[ARIKA]
Sergey... you were my patron?
Please stop this right
now, Your Highness!
This girl is the real Princess!
Princess...?
She is the real
daughter of the King,
and the true heir of Windbloom!
[MASHIRO gasps]
What did you say?
Huh?
[NAGI]
Oh?
I thought you told me you
hadn't found her yet.
Sergey, don't tell me...
...that you've gone
and betrayed me.
No, I just...
[chuckles]
I see how it is.
This isn't like you, getting
all serious about someone.
That's why you'd go to such
lengths to protect that girl.
[gasps]
[NINA]
No... Father...
No...
No!
Well, isn't that interesting?
The Ultimate Black Diamond
reacted to your emotions.
The ones deep in your heart.
What's that legendary
Gemstone doing here?
Okay, Nina,
I'll make you a deal.
If you can stop those girls,
I will forgive Sergey's
little betrayal.
In that case, Nina Wang,
Otome of the Ultimate
Black Diamond,
do you swear to accept
me as your master?
Then hear me, Nina.
In my name, I hereby
release your powers.
You mustn't! Nina!
Materialize!
You haven't been very
fair to me, Father.
You told me that the
one reason I was here
was to become Grand
Duke Nagi's Otome.
That's why I tried so hard.
[NINA]
Tell me, why?
Why? Why are you here, Arika?!
If only you weren't around!
Stop, Nina!
Why? Why do things
have to be this way?
You and I are
friends, aren't we?
Shut up! I don't
care about you!
No!
[screams]
[gasps]
[ARIKA]
Ersty!
[NINA]
Ersty, hang in there!
Talk to me, Ersty!
Why did you...?
Arika... I... I'm so sorry...
I'm sorry, Nina...
To tell the truth...
...it's not...
about the technology.
If only... If only
there was no war...
...I could be together with
everyone... forever...
Ersty!
Erstin!
I'm happy... to have
been... your friend...
That's why... I...
Ersty, no...
Arika...
[yelling]
[screams]
Stop this! Both of you, stop!
Arika!
[NAO gasps]
Oh, no!
[yelling]
[NINA yelling]
[NATSUKI]
I finally got to use my Robe,
but what's with these
new developments?
[SHIZURU] There's not
much we can do about that.
[NATSUKI] What's wrong with me
having some heroic moments?
[SHIZURU] That's true,
but you are really cute
when you're all helpless
like this, Natsuki.
[NATSUKI]
You're so mean to me!
[SHIZURU]
That's a good girl.