[NEFEE sighs]
[NEFEE]
We've completely failed
to fend them off
at the battlefront.
[NEREIS]
But surely the individual
squadrons are doing okay?
[NEFEE]
Well, yes.
But you haven't
reduced enemy numbers
so we can fight
at equal strength.
Don't speak as though you
had nothing to do with it!
You were involved
in this plan as well!
All right, calm down, Nereis.
This is our plan,
and we're both in it together.
[NEREIS]
Besides, how could you predict
that the enemy's mine attacks
would be quite as harsh and
last as long as they did?
Because of that,
our fleet was not in
the best formation
to fight when the enemy
attack vessels arrived.
[NEFEE] The fact that our
flagship needs to participate
in the battle, means
we're in pretty bad shape.
So what do we do next, Nereis?
We could retreat...
But there's no way
you'd do that, is there?
Of course not.
Our forces now completely
surround the Aptic Gate,
and thanks to that,
we're just about managing to
hold them off at the front.
[NEREIS]
If we were to retreat,
that would give the enemy
time to remobilize their fleet.
[NEFEE]
And if we let that happen,
we don't stand a chance.
[NEREIS] Do you want us
to just sit here and wait
while the enemy goes ahead
and destroys us, Nefee?!
[NEFEE]
I was hoping for some evidence
of Spectacular Insanity here.
I'm sorry to disappoint you
but you won't find
any of that in me.
Where do you think you're going?
[NEREIS]
I'm going to have a bath.
Have a bath?
Yes. I'm going to have a bath.
I'm feeling a bit sticky after
all we've been through.
You're not going to
get the best decisions
out of your Commander
if he's exhausted.
We should grab every
opportunity to rest.
Well, yes, I suppose so.
Perhaps you too should
take some time out
and make sure you get some rest.
Hey, aren't you forgetting
something here?
We happen to be in the middle
of a battle right now.
This ship could be destroyed
at any second!
And where's the Commander?
Having a bath?
Killed in action
while having a bath!
It would be a great
dishonor to me to discover
that I'd let my men die in vain.
But at least I would like to
choose where I end my days.
So you make the choice to
die lying in a bathtub?
[gasps]
[LAFIEL]
They're firing at us!
Okay crew, brace yourselves!
This is gonna be tough!
[LAFIEL grunts, sighs]
There's no response
from the laser cannon!
There're breaches in the
hull from sectors 3 to 17,
and the first passageway
has also lost pressure!
The ship's damaged everywhere!
Three crew are dead and
another five wounded!
[SAMSON] The temperature's
rising to dangerous levels!
Any hotter and
the armor will melt!
Request permission to
jettison the armor!
[JINTO]
Explosion in sector 23!
The automatic sprinkler
system has failed!
Things are looking really bad.
Lafiel! Did you hear me?!
[gasps] We've got to
rescue the crew members
who were hurt in the
explosion. Quickly!
Permission is granted to
take any steps necessary.
Just do whatever
you have to do!
I'll try, but the situation
has gotten out of control.
I don't know how much
we can do now!
Deca-Commander Abriel!
Give me a report
on your current situation.
[sighs]
[LAFIEL]
Request permission to withdraw
from the front, Unit Commander.
[ATOSURYUA]
Permission granted, Basroil.
I find the news disappointing,
but it can't be helped.
[LAFIEL]
It's truly disappointing...
[LAFIEL] Wing Aviator!
Can we save the ship?
[SAMSON]
It's almost impossible.
Right now, we're
barely holding on.
If we dislodge the
anti-matter fuel tank,
we can perhaps save
the main body,
but there's no way we can
do it automatically.
We'd have to do it manually,
and the reduced numbers
of the crew mean-- Damn!
Why did we have to go
and lose him as well?
[LAFIEL]
I'm left with no choice...
All crew! Abandon ship!
The Calike's still
in working order?
Yeah, no damage.
Senior Aviator,
get the Calike prepared
immediately for departure!
Yes, Captain!
Supply Officer, get the crew
out of here onto the Calike.
Yes, Captain!
[LAFIEL]
It doesn't seem possible...
This is something I never
thought I'd have to do.
[alarm blares]
All crew! This is the Captain!
You are temporarily discharged
from your responsibilities.
Abandon your posts
immediately and move quickly
to the Calike deck. I repeat!
You are temporarily discharged
from your responsibilities...
Could you do me
a favor, Ekuryua?
Any chance you could
go and get Diaho?
He's in my room.
I've already put him
in his travel carrier.
That's a relief!
I'll go and prepare the
Calike for boarding now.
I don't think there's much
more for me to do up here. So,
do you mind if I go give
Supply Officer Lin a hand?
I'd like to check up on
the members of my crew
who were injured
in the explosion.
As I said before, just do
whatever you have to do.
Well, all right then.
In that case, I'll get
down there right away.
[LAFIEL]
You had a short life, Basroil.
Forgive me.
[LAFIEL groans]
[LAFIEL] It's obvious that we
don't have very much time left.
[CREW MEMBERS shouting]
[NEFEE]
How bad are the losses?
[DEFENSE FLEET COMM. CHIEF]
Over 45% per cent, sir.
[NEFEE sighs]
So this is it...
This is what it's come to.
[ATOSURYUA] All right, we're
going to protect the rear.
I want the Neeroil
to go out in front!
Captain! The enemy
fleet is retreating!
[gasps]
[NEFEE] Hmm... That was
faster than expected.
The main fleet, commanded
by his Highness.
[KENESH] It looks like the enemy
surrounding the Aptic Gate
has decided to make a
definite move to retreat.
So they've finally given up
the struggle, have they?
[KENESH] We're now in a position
to force the enemy into a battle
before they can leave
the area near the gate.
Having said that, there are
no guarantees that we'd win.
[DUSANYU] Of course, if the
battle resulted in a tie...
...strategically it
would be no different
than if we'd lost.
We have to avoid that.
Well, well...
Would you look at that?
Is there something wrong,
your Highness?
[DUSANYU]
Can you see the formation
the enemy's beginning
to move into?
This could be a bit of
a challenge for us.
No, I don't think so.
They're just choosing
the fastest way out,
straight through the middle.
[DUSANYU]
Of course they are.
If we were to simply let them
pass through without
provocation,
our losses would be
kept to a minimum.
Or even better,
we could withdraw our fleet
from the area altogether,
thus avoiding the need
to fight and Aptic would
still remain in the
hands of the Empire.
That way we could also
keep Mystel in the Empire.
Is that what you're
really planning to do?
[DUSANYU]
Hmph. Of course not!
You forget that I
am an Abriel and I
have the pride of an Abriel.
We have assembled
a large fleet of ships,
and coming this far to gain
control of a couple of
out of the way planets
isn't my idea of success.
The enemy has given us
the choice of whether
we fight or whether we don't.
You don't know that for sure.
It doesn't matter whether
I'm sure or not.
It's a fact that we
have that choice
whether or not it's the
one the enemy intended.
We're going to engage
them, understand?
I suppose if I disagree
with that course of action
you'll fire me on the spot?
Come on, you know
I wouldn't do that!
You're the best
Chief of Staff I have!
There's no question of you
being dismissed from your job.
Although, I'll think
twice before I listen
to any of your
opinions from now on.
I thought you might say that.
As it happens,
I have no intention
of disagreeing with you.
Like you said,
we've come this far
to eliminate the enemy fleet
and it would be a shame
to go home without
achieving that goal.
Very well.
The Third Fleet will maintain
its present position.
We'll have the Second and Fourth
Fleets form a cluster formation
and attack the enemy from
the side and from behind.
We'll station the
First Fleet out in front.
The Guard ships will hold
their ground for now,
ready to respond to
any enemy retaliation.
This is only a rough plan.
But until we see how the enemy
organize themselves,
it's a start.
I'd like you to take
a good look
at the efficacy of this
battle strategy.
Roger. Understood.
By the way. There
was something else
I wanted to get confirmation
from you about.
Yes? What was that?
Which one was it?
Which brother did you
have a relationship with?
Was it Nereis?
Or was it Nefee?
[KUFADIS]
Commander in Chief!
The First Fleet has now
completed its deployment.
Thank you for your effort in
getting me that information.
Distance to the enemy
frontline: 120.
They appear to be in
an oval-shaped formation
and all ships are facing
in this direction.
Their patrol ships appear
to be ready to attack
as well as forming
a protective shell
for the ships
inside in the oval.
If we're going to have any
chance of success in this battle
our primary task, as the First
Fleet, will be to break through
that shell and destroy
the weaker ships.
[SPOOR] No, no! Where's
the elegance in that?
[sighs] It may come
as a surprise to you,
but I actually quite enjoy
making mincemeat of those
weaker than myself.
[KUFADIS]
That doesn't surprise me at all.
I mean, trampling over frail,
clapped out assault vessels
and annihilating ships
that have run out of ammunition
can be a quite a beautiful
thing to be part of.
Something almost artistic
about it, don't you think?
Not everyone would agree.
Surely it's a matter of taste?
My dear Chief of Staff,
haven't you realized there's
nothing more important
in this galaxy than my taste?
[KUFADIS]
She's gotta be joking...
I hope she's joking!
[SPOOR] Well, that and having
25 patrol ship squadrons
get together and fight
to the bitter end
using only brute force.
But what other approach
can we take?
We've got to fight this battle
whether we like it or not!
If it were up to me, I'd avoid
the battlefield altogether.
However, we better
stay put here in Aptic.
[KUFADIS] But if we do that,
surely that means
we won't be able to fight
the decisive battle?
[SPOOR] I'm not saying
it's an ideal situation.
But it's got to be better
than the alternative...
I suppose...
All right then.
I guess I ought to stop
grumbling about it
and do something.
Chief of Staff?
Give instructions to all
contingents under our command.
Let the supply forces
stand down
and advance with
surveillance troops only.
Tell all ships to prepare for
battle in regular space.
We'll enter the
space-time bubbles
in small groups of
half squadrons.
The top priority for the
following squadrons will be
to stop the enemy from advancing
any further: Kuryudas, Biruka,
Kengafu, Goshitol, Ferutoni,
Saidoo, and Torarisuto.
Inform them immediately.
I want the other squadrons
to focus on penetrating
the main body of
the enemy fleet.
They are to avoid
engaging in battle
with enemy patrol ships.
Even if provoked,
I insist they wait to retaliate.
If they enter our
space-time bubbles
they'll fight until
they've returned
to the safety of
their own ranks.
We will break through the
outer shell of patrol ships
to cut deep into enemy lines.
[KUFADIS] She plans to
demoralize these guys
no matter what!
The signal to commence
the attack will be
when our space-time bubble
moves forward. Got that?
Yes, ma'am. Understood!
I'll relay the order immediately
to all ships under your command.
The communication ship has
started space-time fusion
with the Saidoo squadron
at the rear of the fleet.
Notify the captain
without delay!
The space-time bubble is
now totally mobile,
on a course of zero-one-zero.
[grunts]
I'm not sure I feel up
to this right now.
[KENESH] The First Fleet
has begun to advance.
In that case, we should
start our advance, as well.
I'll give the order for
squadrons on the frontline
of battle to launch their
mobile space-time mines.
First wave. Space-time
separation complete!
Second wave. Space-time
[CREW 12C]
Third wave.
Space-time separation complete!
The Third Fleet has
begun their mine attack!
[CREW 12C] The space-time
bubbles which appear to be
enemy guard ships
have begun to retreat!
[CREW 12D] Distance to enemy
fleet is now 10...
...9...
...8...7...
...6...
...5...4...
...3...2...
...1!
[CREW 12D]
We've made contact!
I can almost hear the sound of
metal scraping against metal.
[SPOOR] The sound of my dear
ships being damaged.
The sound of my
precious men dying.
It's not a sound I
could ever enjoy...
I guess you'll just have
to get used to it.
[sighs] How true.
A pertinent observation.
[CREW MEMBERS shouting]
[shouting continues]
[CREW screaming]
[FLEET COMM. CHIEF]
We've passed through
the front line of enemy
patrol ship squadrons!
[SPOOR]
Heh.
Notify headquarters!
And inform Futune
and Skuni as well!
All ships prepare to launch
another mine attack!
[KUFADIS]
She looks so happy about this.
[SPOOR]
Once mines are deployed,
all ships must separate into
individual space-time bubbles!
[FLEET COMM. CHIEF]
All mines are now ready
to be launched!
In that case, fire!
[KUFADIS] All mines have been
successfully launched!
[SPOOR] Mobilize individual
space-time bubbles!
Let's go, get 'em!
Have we got everyone on board?
Actually, we're still waiting
for Second Aviator Ekuryua.
She hasn't arrived yet?
[SOBAASH] She had to go
back and get Diaho
but it's taking longer
than expected.
She should be here any moment.
But at least we know
where she is, unlike...
You mean we're missing
someone else?
[SOBAASH] Mm-hm. We had
to leave Paveryua behind
because of his injuries.
Supply Officer Lin
went to rescue him,
but we think he may
have got into some
sort of accident
on his way there.
His pressure helmet
malfunctioned,
so we can't tell where he is
or what's wrong with him.
My guess is he's probably
near the area of Sector One.
That's if he's still alive...
What about Paveryua?
[SOBAASH]
We think he managed to escape
using one of the
emergency pods.
Okay. I'm going back to try
and help Supply Officer Lin.
I want you to take
control of the Calike,
try to pick up Paveryua
in his emergency pod.
But Captain...?!
That's an order, Senior Aviator!
Look after that, will you?
[SOBAASH sighs]
I don't think I have
much choice.
Your Highness, you have
always been a captain
of courage and honor
on board the Basroil.
Please remember that I hold
you in the greatest affection.
Thank you. I leave my
crew in your hands.
Please, take care of them.
It would be an honor.
After all, they are
my crew, too.
[SAMSON]
Captain!
We've only got about
five minutes!
Although I wouldn't be surprised
if this thing blew
at any second.
If after five minutes you still
haven't found the boy...
I know it's difficult, but we'll
have to give up the search.
Please take care.
I don't want to be remembered
as the Senior Aviator
who abandoned her Captain in
the midst of her first battle.
[LAFIEL]
That won't be necessary.
I have every intention of coming
out of this thing alive.
Just make sure you remember
to pick up our emergency pods
once we're done!
We'll be there for
you, Captain!
[SAMSON]
Senior Aviator!
[SOBAASH]
Mm?
[SAMSON]
We've got a problem...
I can't get any more output
from the engine in the Calike!
[gasps] We can't
get out of here?!
We're fighting against
the clock now!
We gotta do somethin' fast,
before she blows up!
[SOBAASH]
Let me come and help!
[SAMSON]
Hurry!
[SOBAASH grunts]
[grunts]
[JINTO]
I was... What was I...?
Huh?!
[JINTO]
Paveryua, where are you?!
Are you in there?!
Huh?
[JINTO]
The emergency pod's been used.
That must mean he was
able to get out of here.
[sighs] Thank goodness!
[JINTO]
Huh?!
[JINTO screams]
[JINTO]
Oh. That was a close one...
I couldn't have been
out for more than
about five minutes.
But that five minutes
could just cost me my life.
[JINTO]
How typical!
I try to act like a hero,
and what do I achieve?
Nothing.
You would think I would have
learned my lesson by now!
Okay. There are no
emergency pods left.
No more pressure helmets.
The pressure in the next sector
is probably 5000 daj.
Oh, and the ship is
about to explode.
There's only one thing
left to for me to do...
But if I call for help, I'm
just gonna get someone else
mixed up in this, and risk
their life as well as mine.
[clattering]
[JINTO]
Huh?
[JINTO grunts]
[inhales]
[coughs]
[panting]
Are you all right, Jinto?
I was okay before
all this happened...
But I'm not sure anymore--
what do you think?
Don't be such an idiot.
Would you have preferred
if I left you?
Of course not!
If you hadn't come,
I'd probably be dead
by now! Thank you.
[LAFIEL] Hurry up.
We don't have much time.
[LAFIEL] What is it with you and
your fascination with vacuums?
[JINTO]
Gimme a break!
They don't mean anything to me.
Believe or not, Landers like me
have this odd preconception
that vacuums aren't
good for your health.
But it's probably just
an old wives' tale.
[LAFIEL]
Huh?
[LAFIEL, JINTO grunt]
[LAFIEL, JINTO panting]
[LAFIEL] Come on,
we can't waste any time.
I think there's some emergency
pods left over there.
I'm sorry.
[LAFIEL]
You know...
Do you remember when you
said to me that you didn't think
anyone would feel sad or
miss you when you died,
and you'd be forgotten?
Yeah. I think so...
[LAFIEL]
Well...
Got it!
Let's go!
[gasps]
[screams]
It's okay, I've got her!
Let's get outta here!
What's happened to the captain
and Supply Officer Lin?
[gasping]
They can't be... Captain. Jinto.
[JINTO]
O Stars, listen to our plea,
Thy kin whose lives
are but short;
We ask that you might guide us;
Lead us throughout eternity.
It's funny, but I really don't
mind being trapped in here.
Probably...
It's probably because
I'm here with you.
[LAFIEL]
You fool.
[JINTO]
I wonder who I really am...