Huh? So! You've got an Abh
cat with a good pedigree?
And it's a Kutirowaru?
If you don't mind,
I'd like to give you some advice
about taking care of him.
If you're going to keep him on
board, then you should really
attach a transmitter
to his collar.
That way, if there's
ever an emergency
you can find him quickly
and he'll be less likely
to come to a sticky end.
Well, you're lookin' pretty
healthy, aren't you?
Good muscles and everything!
This is the same cat
that belongs to Supply
Officer Lin, isn't it?
You know, I think the fact
that the kid even thought
of bringing a cat on board,
let alone actually doing it,
was a stroke of genius!
[laughs]
The Senior Aviator told me
you were worried about Diaho.
I think you'll find
this will help.
What is it? A transmitter.
I can understand you
wanting to have a pet
when we're on patrol
and have lots of free time,
but we're going
into battle soon!
And you're not gonna have
time to look after him.
And he's going to
get in the way.
[JINTO] There's nothing
I can do about that.
The Basroil 's my home.
There's nowhere else
for Diaho to go.
[LAFIEL]
Are you still alive, Jinto?
[JINTO gasps]
[LAFIEL, JINTO grunt]
[LAFIEL grunts]
[LAFIEL]
You know...
When you're lying there asleep,
you kind of look like
you might be dead.
That's a grim way
of putting it!
Wouldn't "unconscious"
be more accurate?
Heh! I was having this dream.
Everyone was there.
And I saw the body of
Klasbul lying in his coffin.
I never imagined I'd
experience being a corpse
while I'm still alive.
[LAFIEL]
Does it still hurt?
[JINTO]
It's just a scratch.
[LAFIEL] Oh, it's humiliating
to ride in a ship
with no exterior area
sensors or guhakes.
[JINTO] This is not a ship.
It's a coffin.
C-O-F-F-I-N.
[LAFIEL]
It's cramped in here.
I suddenly have the urge
to get away from you.
[JINTO]
Ouch! Be careful, I'm injured.
[LAFIEL]
I thought it was just a scratch.
[JINTO exhales]
[LAFIEL]
Jinto.
[JINTO]
Yeah?
[LAFIEL]
Please forgive me.
[JINTO]
For what?
Hey, Jinto...
Huh?
Don't forget that you're
an honorable man...
Hey, Jinto, what's up?
[JINTO]
Uh. Nothing.
I was just thinking
how comfortable
this emergency pod is compared
to that coffin we got stuck in!
[LAFIEL]
But it only gives us 24 hours.
[JINTO] I'm sure Sobaash will
have rescued us before then.
[LAFIEL]
Of course she will!
[JINTO] Why're you so
angry all of a sudden?
[LAFIEL]
I'm not angry!
[JINTO laughs]
[LAFIEL]
What's so funny?
[JINTO]
Nothing really.
When you get angry like that
I guess I feel kind of relieved,
isn't that weird?!
[meows]
[EKURYUA] Can I pick him up?
He looks like he needs a cuddle.
Oh, sure. Thanks!
I guess I've been a careless
owner by neglecting him!
[EKURYUA]
Tell that to the cat!
No, that's okay.
He neglects me too
most of the time,
so we've got a lot in common.
[EKURYUA]
I see...
He'll come back soon,
you'll see.
Now the Basroil 's gone, I've
got nowhere I can call home.
Jinto.
[JINTO]
O Stars, listen to our plea,
Thy kin whose lives
are but short;
we ask that you might guide us.
Lead us throughout eternity.
[JINTO] It's funny,
but I really don't mind
being trapped in here.
Probably...
I'm sure it's because
I'm here with you.
[LAFIEL]
You fool.
[JINTO] I wonder...
who I really am...
[JINTO]
And then, 12 hours after
the Basroil had been destroyed,
we were finally rescued.
I really hope you
enjoyed your bath.
It wasn't bad, thank
you for asking.
Although it was rather annoying
that each time the ship fired
a weapon the water
splashed in my face.
Anything happen
I should know about?
No, there's nothing
much to report.
Except that the enemy retreated.
Oh, and it appears that
the main fleet has arrived.
What did you say?!
That's important! Why didn't
you inform me immediately?!
You've never liked having
your bath disturbed,
even as a kid.
You always ended up
being totally grumpy.
Only if someone was dragging
me out for no reason.
It's completely different when
it's a matter this urgent!
I'll remember that.
But even if I'd told
you right away,
you couldn't have done
anything about it, could you?
I'm the Commander in Chief
and the person who
decides that is me!
Now let's go get the enemy!
I thought you might
get all dramatic
and say something like that.
And that's why I didn't come
and get you out of your bath.
What do you mean by that?
Our fleet is in ruins
from the last battle.
If we go after them now,
it's going to mean
certain death for all of us.
Nothing like that's
going to happen.
[NEREIS sighs]
All right then.
I give in this time, Nefee.
We can't think about winning
or losing at the moment.
We have to regroup and
re-establish our forces
and let the main fleet deal
with the enemy.
[NEREIS]
That's all we can do?
"That's all we can do"?
Listen to yourself!
It's a tough job ahead!
And we're the ones who've got
to see this fleet through it.
We're the ones in charge!
By the way, Nereis.
What now?
You might as well go back
and finish having your bath.
[CREW chattering]
[chattering continues]
[DUSANYU]
That's just like Beneej.
She has forcefully changed
her tactics in order to get
maximum advantage from
any weakness in the enemy.
And she thinks the Abriel
family fights rough!
All things considered,
her method of fighting is just
as violent as anybody else's.
But her strategy
is proving to be
extremely effective, isn't it?
Oh, please spare me.
If you're going to compliment
the head of the Spoor family,
at least have the grace
to do it out of my presence
so that I don't
have to hear it.
[KENESH]
It's not exactly a compliment.
Merely a realistic observation.
Anyway, we've got
the enemy confused
as a result of her tactics.
Yes, but she's left the
Allies confused as well.
We're passing through the rear
of the enemy formation now.
Do you think we destroyed
their ships too quickly?
Huh?!
[KUFADIS] Maybe she
regrets doing it now...
As I was saying, our main
squadrons will be passing
through the rear section
of the enemy fleet shortly.
But only two squadrons
have managed
to keep pace with us.
Shall we give
ourselves a little rest?
Seems like a good idea.
I don't see any reason why not.
[SPOOR]
All right then, we'll do that.
Relay this order
to the captains:
place your space-time bubbles
into stationary mode.
However, should a
situation arise,
give them permission to alter
the space-time bubbles
into a mobile state
at their own discretion.
[KUFADIS]
Roger!
It is a good thing
for us that the enemy
has already used up
their supply of mines.
They were obviously confident
that they would recapture Aptic.
[DUSANYU] That's probably
not the only reason.
Their confidence also came from
using new fleet formations
and their increased
number of patrol ships.
[KENESH]
That could be true.
[DUSANYU gasps]
[DUSANYU]
Contact the ships
in the Assault Vessel
Mudoto Contingent.
Tell them to pull out of
the battlefield immediately.
Their losses are too great.
[KENESH]
Roger.
[DUSANYU] The same goes for
Konaseeru and Garikoosh.
[KENESH] That means that
a total of 11 squadrons
will have been withdrawn.
I was prepared for some losses,
but this is terrible.
Yes, I'm afraid it is terrible.
Actually, your Highness,
I think you're doing
rather well.
Although the enemy
had far more ships than us,
we've managed to fight them
and still maintain control
of the battlefield.
[DUSANYU]
That's good of you to say so.
However, if those other
fleets were to arrive soon
our situation would
improve considerably.
[KENESH] You mean Admiral Rulef
with the Second Fleet,
and Admiral Kotoponi
with the Fourth Fleet?
[DUSANYU] I wonder what
those two are doing?
They're on their way,
aren't they?
It looks to me as though
the two fleets are advancing
towards us as quickly as the
laws of physics allow them to.
[sighs] Don't you hate physics?
They can really get
in the way sometimes.
[DUSANYU laughs]
Oh, your Highness!
You know I've always been
a loyal Chief of Staff
on board this ship.
I suppose I should
ignore that rather silly
comment of yours.
Yes. I don't know exactly
to whom you are loyal.
But if you could see fit
to ignore my musings,
that would be the best
thing for the both of us.
I'm sorry. I shouldn't have
questioned your loyalty.
[KENESH]
Right!
Excuse me, sir!
There's a message coming
through from the Second Fleet!
It's Admiral Rulef!
[FLEET OFFICER 1] Distance
to the enemy front: 100 wesdaj!
The First Fleet has
stopped advancing
and now appears to be
gathering its forces together.
We've made it in time!
[TORIIRU] The enemy appears
to be in disarray.
[RULEF]
All right! All ships!
Prepare to fire mobile
space-time mines.
We've got to make up for the
time we lost in getting here!
[FLEET OFFICER 2]
All ships ready to fire
their mobile space-time mines!
[RULEF] After deploying their
mines, all ships are to advance
in individual
space-time bubbles.
Yes, sir!
Standby! All mobile
space-time mines...
...fire!
The Second Fleet has begun
attacking the enemy!
Rest period over!
Notify all ships!
Order their individual
space-time bubbles to mobilize
on a course of 2-7-0!
Transmit the following
message to them:
Follow me!
I might get a bit more fun
bullying these weaklings around.
[KUFADIS] It's not exactly
my idea of fun...
[gasps] She couldn't...
They're a little bit
old fashioned
but there's something about
them, don't you think?
[KUFADIS]
She couldn't possibly say that!
So... Ya lousy pigs
and crawling mud turtles!
Prepare to meet your doom!
[CREW 1D] The Lashkau has
entered space-time fusion!
[CREW 1F] The Seventh
Attack Vessel squadron
has entered space-time fusion!
[CREW 1D]
Fire the electromagnetic cannon!
[CREW 1E] Second Squadron
Kuryuders--spread out!
[CREW 1F]
Roger!
[CREW 1E] Ship 00!
Attack from the right side!
Let's turn the ship
around 180 degrees
and then prepare to fire
the anti-proton cannon!
Maneuver completed!
Fire the anti-proton cannon.
[ENEMY CREW screaming]
[CREW 12D]
Enemy Three and Enemy Nine
are separating from their
space-time bubble!
[CAPTAIN 13A]
Don't let them get away!
There are more space-time
bubbles up ahead on the left!
The Fourth Fleet's
come to help us out!
[SESKARSE]
Enemy Nine, destroyed!
[KOTOPONI]
Fire the electromagnetic cannon
and do not stop.
[SANKAU OFFICER 1]
In addition to the Fourth Fleet,
all the other squadrons
are engaged in combat.
Our ships now outnumber
the enemy forces!
Now the outcome of
this battle is assured.
Could be.
It looks like the enemy
is planning a retreat
into the Wimpel region
What do you intend to do
once that has happened?
[DUSANYU] As soon as the enemy
has withdrawn into Wimpel,
we will seal it off using
front line ships.
Then, once we've
re-established control
of Aptic, Mystel, and Dalmav,
we'll move on and take Neopol
and Malskuty as well.
[KENESH] And you plan to cut off
any remaining enemy forces?
[DUSANYU] We'll let the
Fifth Fleet handle that.
Then we'll be free to
carry on with attacking
more enemy territories.
Understood, your Highness.
[DUSANYU]
Now that's resolved,
there's just one
problem remaining.
Huh? And what's that?
We still don't know which
of the brothers it was...
Was it Nereis that gave you such
heartache, or was it Nefee?
Which was it?!
Your Highness!
I don't know... Was it both of
them together, a double date?
Or could it be
that you don't actually know
which one it was at all.
[KENESH]
Your Highness...
I have devoted half my
life to the Star Forces.
I don't think there's
anybody who doubts
your loyalty and devotion,
but if there is, bring
them here to me.
I'd be perfectly happy to
convince them otherwise.
[KENESH]
I would also like to state
that I love and respect
the Imperial Family.
It gives me a great
deal of pleasure
to know you feel that way.
That being said, I hope you
will understand that it's
extremely difficult for
me to say this to you.
You who are the Commanding
Admiral of the Star Forces
and heir to the Imperial
throne, however...
Yes?
[KENESH growls]
Just shut up!
[JINTO] At last, it looks like I
can get someone to look after
Diaho in the Clyuve Palace.
I thought he was a
pretty friendly cat,
but he just seems to want to sit
around all day doing nothing.
[LAFIEL]
Oh, yeah.
I always wondered why you
and him got along so well.
Now I think I understand why...
[JINTO]
How dare you say that!
[ANNOUNCER 13A] The connection
process is now complete.
All passengers are requested
to board their ships.
[JINTO]
Okay, ready to go?
[LAFIEL] Yes. Now you have
made the arrangements
to send Diaho back
to the Capital?
[JINTO]
Of course!
But I figured Ekuryua would want
to say goodbye to him as well.
So I thought I could bring
Diaho on board just until
we've finished the
initial navigation period.
Then, I'll make sure he gets
where he needs to be.
Don't worry!
I'm not gonna forget about
him and leave him on the ship!
[LAFIEL] Well just make sure
you don't. Understood?
[JINTO]
Okay.
The poor little guy...
He'll probably forget all
about me in no time.
[LAFIEL] I don't think we should
expect anyone to remember us
until the end of our days--
especially not a cat!
[JINTO]
Heh. Good advice.
You know, thinking about it,
in all the time we spent
together on the Basroil,
the only time we fought about
anything was to do with Diaho.
It's kinda weird to say this
when we're in the middle
of a war, but things sure
seem peaceful right now.
[LAFIEL] It's good that you're
feeling peaceful.
And by the way, we never
fought about Diaho.
I never heard you insisting we
should keep him on board.
[JINTO] I guess now that you
mention it, that's true!
I mean, I did think about
saying something,
but it didn't seem important
enough in the middle of a war.
[LAFIEL]
That's silly.
[JINTO] By the way, did you hear
the rumor about the new ships?
Heavy attack vessels.
[LAFIEL] I heard it was
light patrol ships.
[JINTO] Then I bet
it's neither of them!
Probably something
in between the two.
I wonder why they're
giving us ships
that are so awkward to maneuver.
[LAFIEL] Perhaps it's the attack
vessel that's awkward for them,
not the patrol ship.
Maybe they've decided
that they need to upgrade
the fleet for future battles.
[LAFIEL]
But I...
So that's what they've given
us for the new Basroil ?
It's exactly the same
as the last ship.
Of course. Why wouldn't
they give us the same?
Did you have some ulterior
motive in bringing this up?
[JINTO] Well, yeah... I thought
if the ship was big enough,
maybe I could keep the cat...
You fool.
[JINTO laughs]
[JINTO]
We lived on a well-known ship.
But it wasn't well-known
because it had been in a
famous battle or anything.
Its fame came from being home
to two members of royalty.
One of them was our Captain,
Deca-Commander Abriel.
She was a princess of
one of the royal families
of the Humankind Empire Abh.
[JINTO]
The other was me,
Count Jinto of the Lin
Syune Rock Hyde family.
I'm a nobleman.
However, this ship was the
only place I had to call home.
And, if truth be told,
it was the only place
where I felt like I
really belonged.
Welcome home.
It's good to see you, Captain.
Supply Officer Lin.
Please, Captain.
I would like to return this.
Why thank you.
[LAFIEL] This time I intend
to fight better for you.
You should know,
I'm counting on you.
If you're all ready,
let's prepare for
departure right away!
I'm the Empire's Deputy
Representative?
Are you sure?
It's an order straight
from the top.
So you don't have any choice.
[JINTO]
The Aptic Planetary System will
relinquish all rights of
sovereignty over territories
currently controlled
by the United Mankind.
From this day forward,
these territories will
become a part of
the Humankind Empire Abh, and
will be subject to its laws.
[LAFIEL] If the Empire has
made any demands...
[NEREIS]
Hmph. I hadn't realized that
all those famous people
were under my command.
[NEFEE] I know you're
bored by all of this,
but is there any chance
you might be able to tell me
the secret of how you manage
to be so ignorant about
your own fleet?!
[NEREIS] Wasn't that Count
Hyde the same young man
who conquered some
world or other with
Her Highness the
princess a while back?
What do you mean?
The story I heard was that
she successfully conquered
a whole planet armed
only with a laser gun.
I wonder, Nereis, if your
memory might be failing you
or if your source is feeding
you misinformation.
It hardly seems likely that
those stories are true.
Does it really matter
if it's the truth or not?
I always find stories
far more interesting
if they've been created
out of thin air!
You could be right.
Although, I have to say
it's that kind of attitude
that drags our family's
reputation through the mud.
[LAFIEL] Do you swear that you
will not take any action
whatsoever to achieve
independence from the Empire?
No, I won't.
I might permit myself to dream
about it once in a while.
Or is that forbidden as well?
Depressurization complete.
Release the locks on the gates!
[ATOSURYUA]
So. I see you've been released
from your duties as the
Territorial Ambassador.
You know, it's a shame.
You're lucky, because you
can continue taking part
in the original
battle operations.
However, we have to complete
the initial navigation period
on our new ship before
we can join you.
Don't rush into it. The battles
will still be there for you
when you've finished.
I have no doubt there'll be
plenty of opportunities
for us to fight alongside
each other again.
And who knows, I might be
the one who's fighting
under your command by then!
Commander?
[ATOSURYUA] I wish you luck,
Deca-Commander Abriel.
And the next time we end
up fighting together...
Why don't you and I
share a bottle of wine.
It'll be my treat!
[SAMSON]
Gates are fully open!
[LAFIEL]
Request permission to depart.
Senior Aviator--
you care for a drink?
A little somethin' to celebrate
our survival, whaddya say?
That'd would be nice,
Line Wing Aviator!
But do try not to fall
asleep on me this time.
It was hard enough getting you
to sober up last time--
forcing that medicine down
your throat wasn't easy!
Ha, I'll be fine, you'll see!
You brought the cat?
I'm not allowed to bring
him along with us this time.
So I thought you might
like to say goodbye.
I'm sure he'd like you
to play with him.
[EKURYUA]
Mm...
Uh. Well you see, some people
had expressed quite strongly
the view that having
a cat on board ship
wasn't really a good idea
in the first place.
I hope you're not implying that
I'm to blame me for this!
Oh, of course not!
Well, uh. No-- I...
Well, that is what
you said to me!
[JINTO]
I wonder who I am...
I'm still looking for
the answer to that one.
But now there's Lafiel...
Which means there's something
else I need to find.
After you rescued me,
you said to me that...
Well, I need to find the
right words to respond.
Hey, Lafiel... what's the rush?
The words will come
to me someday.
The right words
at the right time.
Until then, I'd like you
to stick around.
Just a little bit longer.
Then, maybe one day, I'll
find the answers I need.
All engines are
fully operational!
Living conditions on
board: operational!
We've been cleared for departure
from the Vobeirunei Naval
Station Control Room.
Preparations for departure
are complete.
Main engine! Start ignition!
Ignition... complete!
This is the new attack
vessel Basroil .
Daisiele!
[LAFIEL]
Are you all right, Jinto?
[JINTO] I was okay
before all this happened,
but I'm not sure anymore.
What do you think?
[LAFIEL]
Don't be such an idiot.
Would you'd have preferred
if I'd left you?
[JINTO]
Of course not.
If you hadn't come, I'd probably
be dead by now! Thank you.
[LAFIEL] What is it with you and
your fascination with vacuums?
[JINTO]
Gimme a break!
They don't mean anything to me.
Believe or not, Landers like me
have this odd preconception
that vacuums aren't
good for your health.
But it's probably just
an old wives' tale!
[LAFIEL]
You know...
Do you remember when you
said to me that you didn't think
anyone would feel sad or
miss you when you died,
and you'd be forgotten?
Yeah. I think so.
[LAFIEL, JINTO groan]
If you'd died back there...
I would have been sorry
that you'd gone.
Is that good enough for you?
[JINTO]
Huh?!
[NARRATOR 2 speaking Baronh]