[NARRATOR speaking in Baronh]
[CREW 9A]
Close the hatches!
[CREW 9B]
Hatches closed!
[CREW 9A]
Prepare to dismantle connecting
passageways and store them.
[CREW 9B] Preparations for
departure  complete.
[CREW 9A] Engage the forward
Stabilization Control Device.
[CREW 9C]
Engaged!
[CREW 9A]
Dismantle the passageways!
[CREW 9C]
Connectors dismantling!
[CREW 9D]
All ships fully operational.
[CREW 9B] Preparations
for departure complete.
[CREW 9C] The Stabilization
Control Device is ready.
[CREW 9A]
Turn on the main engine!
[COMMUNICATIONS OFFICER 9A]
I repeat. The enemy fleet
is expected to enter combat
range within six hours.
All ships are to be
ready for departure.
I repeat. The enemy fleet
is expected to enter combat
range within six hours.
All ships are to be
ready for departure.
Crew stand by for departure!
[SAMSON] All engines
are fully operational.
Reporting no problems
on board the Basroil.
Preparations for
departure are complete.
Disengage the connecting
passageways!
Connecting passageways
being disengaged now.
Turn on the main engine!
Turning on the main engine.
Daisiele!
[DUSANYU] I've had a little bit
of time to think about this.
[KENESH]
Hm.
Relax. It's got nothing to
do the Bebaus brothers.
I knew all about you
having an affair
with one of them
a long time ago.
I suppose that's a relief.
So, what's this all about?
What do you think about us
building up the First Fleet
to make it more substantial?
The First Fleet? Are you sure?
We'd have to gather
together more patrol ships
than we had last time.
[DUSANYU]
Agreed.
I think it's feasible
that we can get hold
of 12 more squadrons.
[KENESH]
Maybe even up to 13.
[DUSANYU] Ha, ha.
Looks like I miscalculated!
I take it you've already
considered this option?
Yes. The staff have
been working on it.
They're prepared for
all eventualities.
It's difficult to predict
the correct course of action
to take because there
are so many uncertain
factors in the equation.
Since we don't know the enemy's
exact strategy, we can't be sure
that increasing the
number of patrol ships
will be the right decision.
[DUSANYU]
But if I go ahead and order
the strengthening of the
First Fleet, you won't object?
[KENESH]
No, I won't.
However, if that's the course of
action you're intending to take,
I've got one piece of advice.
And what's that?
I think we should replace
the Commander-in-Chief.
[DUSANYU]
What's wrong with Beneej?
[KENESH] With all these
extra patrol ships,
she would be in charge
of 25 squadrons.
Now, I'm not concerned
about Admiral Spoor's
ability to command, but such
a high level of responsibility
is not appropriate
to her rank.
Surely someone with a higher
authority should be in charge.
[DUSANYU]
If you're not concerned
about her ability to command,
then I don't see
the problem here.
[KENESH]
I appreciate your point of view.
But there is another problem--
with all these extra squadrons,
the headquarters
of the First Fleet
is going to be short-staffed.
[DUSANYU]
It'll be fine.
It doesn't matter whether
they're controlling
12 squadrons or 25.
[KENESH]
Your Highness...
What is it now?
Seeing as to how you
backed up Admiral Bebaus,
and now the way you're
supporting Admiral Spoor,
I'm wondering if you're
giving members of the root
families preferential treatment
because of their background.
You should know that some
statements are unacceptable.
I do not show favoritism based
on an individual's bloodline.
And even if I did, do you
think I'd run the risk
of letting the head
of the Spoor family
be assigned to such an important
and dangerous mission
without being sure
she could do the job?
Yes, I suppose you're right.
[DUSANYU grunts]
Can't you see that
the way in which
I make my decisions is
perfectly straightforward?
Having Beneej in charge
of this operation
is the most rational choice.
That's all there is
to it, I'm afraid.
And you know,
I wouldn't be at all surprised
if she didn't even want
the responsibility that comes
with doing this job.
I see.
Good. So now I want you
to get in contact
with Beneej for me.
[KENESH]
Understood.
[CREW 9E] One minute to
the rendezvous location.
[CREW 9F]
Turn off the main engine!
[CREW 9G]
Engine off!
[CREW 9F] Engage the
Stabilization Control!
[CREW 9H]
Stabilization Control engaged!
[CREW 9I]
Turn off the main engine!
[CREW 9E] Thirty seconds to the
rendezvous location!
[CREW 9F]
Crew is now dismissed!
[CREW 9K]
Turn off the main engine!
[CREW 9L] Turning off the main
engine now!
[SOBAASH] Arriving at the
rendezvous location now.
[SAMSON] Leaving the
Stabilization Control on.
Turning off the main engine.
All crew are free to step
down from their stations.
I want everyone to keep
an eye on the schedule
and make sure
they get some rest.
[CREW]
Yes, Ma'am!
[JINTO]
Captain.
I just wondered if you'd like
me to get you a drink...?
Yes. I'd like that.
But if you want to be on your
own, that's okay, just tell me.
I don't want you to think
you can't get rid of me!
If you want to stay here
with me, that's fine--
it doesn't bother me.
Is there any chance we
could look at the view?
[LAFIEL]
Mm-hm.
As a kid, I never thought
I'd see a view like this.
Now here I am, looking at
it with my own two eyes.
[LAFIEL]
I always knew I'd see this.
It was decided before I
was born that I would join
the Star Forces,
and that one day I would be
found in the midst of battle.
However, I hadn't anticipated
being the Captain
of an assault ship.
I wanted more than that.
I wanted to wear the
uniform of an Admiral!
[JINTO] You've got a
long road ahead of you.
I'm sure it'll happen someday.
[LAFIEL]
True...
But what about when you
were young, Jinto?
What did you want to be?
[JINTO] I was only 10
when the Empire came
and took control of our planet.
I don't remember wanting
to do anything then.
I was far too young to decide.
But I'm pretty sure
that going into space
wasn't something I'd thought
of as a serious option.
[LAFIEL] Hm. But at least
you had some options.
That's true.
Although back in those
days on our planet,
I don't think there was
much to choose from.
Hold on--there was something!
My mother, before she died,
was a mining engineer.
I decided that was what
I was gonna do as well.
I didn't even know what
a mining engineer did.
[LAFIEL]
So, what do they do?
[laughs] I'm ashamed to
say I still don't know!
Anyway, I'm not
gonna be one now,
so I guess it doesn't matter.
[LAFIEL] I've always wondered
what it would be like
to not know what you're
going to do with your life.
Or what path you're
going to follow.
[JINTO]
It can be unsettling.
Sometimes you have to do
a job you hate just to get by.
On the other hand, that dream
job you've always wanted
might turn out to
be kinda boring.
To be honest with you, I
didn't think very much about
what I wanted to do
when I was a kid.
But I felt relieved
when it was decided
I would become an Abh.
'Cause, as a member of
the Empire's nobility,
I had a course set out for me,
even if I hadn't made
that choice for myself.
That's kinda like me--
I know what I'm going to do.
Whether I like it or not,
I've got the job of
Empress ahead of me.
You don't sound convinced
that being an Empress
is something you want.
What I want has
nothing to do with it.
If you must know,
I really wanted to work
on a merchant ship.
However, as an Abriel,
I have no choice but to take my
place on the Imperial throne.
Maybe afterwards I could
go off and do a real job,
once I've done my duty.
[JINTO] So you went into
the family business.
Things seem to be
so simple for you.
I think I envy that.
[LAFIEL] Don't forget,
you're an Abh, too.
Yes Lafiel,
of course I know that.
If this operation
succeeds, who knows--
maybe the Hyde star
system will end up
being recaptured by
the Empire as well.
[LAFIEL]
Any idea what you'll do
once your territories
are restored?
Uh, not really.
It'd be hard to go back
and meet people again
after being away for so long.
Sometimes I wish I could
give up my title of Count
to somebody else.
[LAFIEL]
You could always hire a deputy.
[JINTO]
I know, but it would feel
like I'm running away,
shirking my responsibilities.
Besides, I don't
have a good excuse.
[LAFIEL] You're working
for the Star Forces!
Isn't that a good enough?
[JINTO]
Possibly...
Anyway, if I've still not gone
back after another 10 years,
maybe I'll be
disqualified as a Count!
[JINTO gasps] Hey!
Why don't we switch titles?!
You can be Countess Hyde,
and I'll be Viscount Paryunu!
I could spend all my time
growing roses somewhere!
Forget it.
There's no way you could
do something like that.
S'pose you're right.
Seemed like a good
idea at the time.
Although, I might've ended up
with the nickname
"Viscount of the Roses"!
I'm not really sure that
would have suited me!
[LAFIEL] You seem to forget
that being a Count is a duty.
[JINTO] It's a duty
I'd happily give away
if there was anyone
willing to take it!
The noble title of Count Hyde
belongs to your family.
It's not possible
to give it away.
[JINTO]
I know. It's like it haunts me!
And you know what's worse?
I'm the only surviving
member of the Lin family.
So it's all up to me.
If I had a cousin somewhere,
I'd give the title to him.
Well then, you should
stay in the Star Forces,
or maybe work on
a merchant ship.
Many nobles who don't want to
live in their own territory
end up doing that.
[JINTO]
Really?
Then maybe that's what I'll do.
But, I don't want
the people back home
to think I'm chickening
out or anything.
[LAFIEL] There are pros
and cons to everything.
It's up to you to decide.
[JINTO] Hey, thanks
for the conversation.
It was helpful.
When I became an Abh,
I was worried that
my whole life would
be planned for me.
But it's nice to know
you can have fun, too!
Yes. Even nobles
need to have fun.
We, as Abhs, have
three stages of life
to experience before
we can become adults.
You and I have only
started the first stage,
and we need to make the most
of each part of the journey.
Why worry about the future?
Let's make the most of today.
Well, I don't think I spend that
much time worrying about it.
So what are these
"three stages of life"
you were talking about?
I think I know what
two of them are.
One would be spending
time as a pilot,
another spending
time as a merchant.
But what's the third?
Can't you take a guess?
I haven't got a clue.
It's the most important
of the three of them.
C'mon, tell me what it is!
When you become a parent...
[DUSANYU]
Hello, Beneej!
I see you got yourself
a new hairdresser?
[SPOOR]
No.
If you must know,
you caught me
just as I was going
to sleep, your Highness.
I apologize for any
inconvenience caused.
[SPOOR] It's always an
honor to receive a call
from you, your Highness.
No matter what time
of day or night it is.
Now then, what can I do for you?
Interesting.
From what you've said, I can see
the possibility that our fleet
will have to engage in combat
with the enemy's elite squadron
of patrol ships.
There is that possibility, yes.
[SPOOR] I thought my
fleet was to provide
an elegant finish to the battle.
You weaken the enemy,
then our cute-looking ships
come along and
clean up the mess.
Unfortunately, our
expectations must change.
Depending on the
enemy's actions.
Squadrons of patrol ships
fighting head-to-head
is a far from elegant
way to fight a battle.
It's barbaric!
Surely there must be
a way headquarters
can figure out an
alternative strategy?
We'll try and do
our best for you.
But in the end, it's
more important to win
even if it's done barbarically.
Who cares how
elegantly you fight
the battle if you don't win.
You're forcing me to
undertake this mission
in a style usually
associated with the Abriels.
You know, your Highness,
you're a very unkind man.
And now to bed...
How interesting that Beneej
should call me unkind.
Should I be annoyed by that?
Or do you think coming from her
it's some kind of compliment?
Don't ask me--I've got no idea.
[SPOOR] I just can't seem
to keep my big mouth shut
when I'm speaking
to his Highness!
I mean, I know
Abriels are famous
for being terribly serious.
It's always fun to tease them
and try and provoke a reaction.
But this guy... He simply
doesn't take the bait!
It's impossible to tease
him about anything!
It may surprise you to learn
that being teased by you
is not the royal family's
only function.
It might be that they have
better things to do
with their time.
Well, my dear Chief of Staff,
I can't say I've
seen anything
to back up your opinion so far.
[CREW 9A] Preparations to
fire the space-time mines
from the front-line battle
ships are complete.
All ships working in the
vicinity of the front-line
battle ships must
now clear the area.
I repeat! All ships
working in the vicinity
of the front-line battle ships
must now clear the area.
[CREW 9B] Front-line ships--
launch space-time mines!
[CREW 9C]
Space-time mines launched!
[CREW 9D]
Space-time mines... launched.
[OFFICER 9A]
Space-time mines are ready
to be positioned for detonation!
[ATOSURYUA]
The battle is about to begin.
I need you to relay an
urgent message to all units!
All crew are to take up
their positions immediately!
[SECOND OFFICER]
Roger!
[CREW 9M] Assault Vessel
Latouche Contingent!
All ships to take up
battle positions!
[CREW 9N] Assault Vessel
Latouche Contingent!
[CREW] All ships to
take up battle positions!
[CREW chattering]
[CREW] All ships to take
up battle positions!
[CREW chattering]
All ships to take up
battle positions!
I repeat... Assault Vessel
Latouche Contingent!
All ships to take up
battle positions!
[CREW chattering]
[CREW 9N] Supply Vessel
Jyosoryusuruu Contingent!
All ships to take up
battle positions!
[DEFENSE FLEET CHIEF]
All ships are in position!
Enemy fleet arriving
in 30 minutes!
[NEREIS]
So, our main fleet is over here.
I guess if we wait for them,
they might arrive in
another 50 hours or so.
[NEFEE]
The enemy must know that, too.
They'll come at us
with all they've got.
Good. I wouldn't have
it any other way.
This war isn't happening
solely for the benefit
of your entertainment,
you know.
Believe me when I say
that I'm not trying
to turn this war into
a game. However,
if we do happen
to enjoy ourselves,
where's the harm in that?
If you say so.
[NEREIS] Besides, we have the
lives of our crew at stake here.
You must be crazy if you think
I'd actually change our plans
for the sake of a little
bit of entertainment.
[NEFEE] Actually, that is
what I'm worried about.
But I hope you won't forget
what you just said.
After all, we don't want
our family's reputation
to sink any lower
than it is already...
Or perhaps that should
be we don't want it
to get any higher.
[NEREIS] Don't worry.
I'm not going to do anything
to enhance the Bebaus
family's notoriety
for Spectacular Insanity.
In fact, all that it would
take to make me happy
would a normal life.
[NEFEE] So, being an Admiral
and commanding a fleet
is your idea of a normal life?
You know, I think your attitude
has just proved beyond the
shadow of a doubt that
you suffer from our
family's affliction more than
you realize, my dear brother!
In that case, my advice would be
to stop spending so much time
worrying about it. Otherwise,
I might get the urge
to add yet another
chapter to the history
of our Spectacular Insanity.
Don't worry, Brother.
I'm going to be here with you.
If worse comes to worst,
I'll stop you doing that.
Even if it means killing you.
Now that does make
me worry, Nefee.
I don't really have
a problem with you
getting rid of me that way,
but I'd've hoped it
would have been in
slightly more edifying
circumstances.
Transmission received
from the Koosururu!
The enemy has launched
several space-time bubbles
that we suspected are mines!
[NEREIS] While we were
wasting time talking,
the enemy has made
the first move.
What's the estimated
time of arrival?
About seven minutes.
Should we counterattack
with our own mines?
We don't have much
choice in the matter.
We can't let them tear us apart
without some retaliation.
At last, you're making
some sense, Nereis.
Thank you very much.
Fire all mines directly
into the Sord!
Issue this order
to the entire fleet!
So, the battle has begun...
[SOBAASH] All mines have
now entered the Sord!
[LAFIEL]
So many mines...
Makes you feel defenseless.
Come to think of it, we've been
defenseless from the start.
Whether it's one
mine or a hundred,
this ship's armor is
so thin that one hit
would finish us.
It's going to be impossible
for our side to destroy
all of those enemy mines.
So it's a safe bet that
some of them will end up
making their way towards us.
[LAFIEL]
Keep calm...
You have the fate of 20
lives lying in your hands...
[gasps]
Officers have a
responsibly to their crew.
Senior Aviator, do you
remember the mines
that misfired in Wimpel?
Will that happen again?
I don't know. I was thinking
exactly the same thing.
Why are you concerned
about that?
On that occasion, I thought
we'd destroyed all the mines
that had been launched.
That's right.
But then we realized
what was inside
those two space-time bubbles.
There were seven mines in there
that were ready to explode.
The enemy's...
...new weapon?
[beeping]
[gasps]
[SOBAASH] The enemy mines
at the head of the formation
are due to arrive at any second!
They're here. They're
right in front of us!
It's hard to tell what that is.
Second Aviator!
I want you to keep
a close eye on it!
Yes, Captain!
Line Wing Aviator.
Are we ready to go?
Oh, yes, we're ready--
can't you feel the atmosphere in
here bubbling with excitement?!
We can move forward at any
time, with maximum speed!
In that case...
...let the battle commence!
So, first on the scene
is the Basroil.
They sure have a lot of
energy and enthusiasm.
I wonder if that has to do
with her being an Abriel.
I'm sorry, but I'm afraid I
can't let Your Imperial Highness
take all the glory
in this battle.
[sighs] Now keep calm, Lafiel.
[LAFIEL] Prepare to fire
the anti-proton cannon!
Preparations to fire
the anti-proton cannon
are now complete!
[JINTO]
The three stages of life...
And I'm only at the first.
I'm not gonna give up
until I've had the chance
to experience all three!
[SOBAASH]
The enemy mines
will be within firing
range in 10 seconds.
8...
...7...6...
...5...
...4...3...
...2...
...1...
Enemy mine is now
within firing range!
Fire the anti-proton cannon!
Their new weapon?
I hope you're not fooling
around with me about this.
[LAFIEL]
It's almost like...
...their spirits... have gone.