[JINTO]
We had been sent on a mission
to patrol the region
around the Wimpel Gate.
There we were searching
for any enemy
reconnaissance ships belonging
to the United Mankind.
However,
once the enemy had
arrived, we were forced
to retreat into Plane Space
and were trying
to get back to base
when we ran out of fuel.
But at the last minute,
we were saved by the intuition
of our Captain, Lafiel.
Those space-time
bubbles are our allies.
I'm sure of it.
We must continue to advance!
[JINTO]
Even though we had been plucked
from the jaws of death,
we didn't even get a chance
to catch our breath.
The next target for the forces
of the United Mankind,
which had attacked us
at the Wimpel Gate,
was gonna be right here.
In the Aptic region.
[DUSANYU] So the main
enemy forces have moved
into the Wimpel region?
[KENESH]
Yes. Reconnaissance ships
have confirmed the situation.
Well in that case, it seems
that Aptic is the
enemy's primary target.
[KENESH]
I expect so.
And do we know...
the strength of their fleet?
Approximately 170 squadrons
of assault ships,
give or take 15 contingents.
[DUSANYU]
Isn't that lower than expected?
[KENESH]
In terms of assault ships, yes,
but they appear to have more
patrol ships than we assumed.
[DUSANYU]
Hmm....
Perhaps they learned
their lesson
from the battle three years ago,
which ended in a draw.
[KENESH]
What lesson?
Do you mean it's better
tactically to build up a force
with more patrol ships
than attack vessels?
[DUSANYU] It's possible that's
what they may have decided.
There are even some factions
within our own ranks who
are demanding just that.
[KENESH] You're not
suggesting that the enemy
has learned their lesson from
that battle and we haven't?
[DUSANYU]
I don't know.
I'm not sure that
the enemy's decision
is necessarily correct.
But if they do have
a lot of patrol ships
it seems like a waste of
resources to fight them
with our attack vessels--as with
our previous interception
of their reconnaissance mission.
[KENESH] You make it sound
as though attack vessels
would be useless in
the upcoming battles.
[DUSANYU] If an enemy can
gather as many patrol ships
together as this one
appears to have done,
our attack vessels
may not be much use.
[KENESH] In which case,
we've been provided
with fighting resources that
are practically redundant.
[DUSANYU]
I suppose so...
[DUSANYU laughs] I don't think
we should register a complaint
until we return to
the Imperial Capital.
Until then, we'll
have to make do
with what we have
available to us.
[KENESH] But that severely
reduces our chance of victory.
[DUSANYU]
We knew that from the start.
We have to keep our
fingers crossed that
the Bebaus brothers do
their part of the job well.
How about moving some forces
in from the Mystel region?
There'll be no need to do that.
Even if Aptic is going to end up
being the main battlefield,
we shouldn't do anything to
loosen our hold on Mystel.
I understand all of that,
but surely you--
Why are you so worried
about leaving Admiral
Bebaus to handle this?
I know their family can act
a little eccentric at times,
but you can always trust their
ability on the battlefield.
Certainly Nereis, anyway.
Besides, he has an excellent
Chief of Staff to support him.
But that "excellent"
chief of staff
is also a part of
the Bebaus family!
[DUSANYU] Hm. It's becoming
apparent that you find it
difficult to trust our
admiral and his brother.
Did you have some sort of...
bad experience in the past
that caused you
to feel this way?
I don't want to answer
that question.
Very well, if you
insist, I understand.
You don't have an issue with
them personally, do you?
I've already said I don't want
to answer that question.
You've made that obvious.
So tell me.
Is it the admiral
or the chief of staff
that you have a problem with?
[KENESH]
I've told you...
...I don't want to
talk about it!
So let's just change
the subject!
Very well, as you wish.
Anyway...
...I'll be in my room.
This is something
I need to spend
some time thinking about.
Call me if anything comes up.
Your Excellency,
what did you mean
when you said you've
got to think about it?
I'm not going to tell you!
We're running out of coolant
for the propellants?
[OFFICER 8A] Yes, sir.
We have less than 70%
of what is
considered sufficient.
That's not even
enough for our fleet
to undertake a battle
in regular space.
[NEREIS]
I see.
Of course, we do
have lots of water
that can be used in
place of a coolant.
Where is it?
Right over there!
[NEREIS] Contact the government
there, and start organiz--
[NEFEE]
We can't.
What do you mean
"we can't"? Why not?
Because the government of
the Aptic Planetary System
still hasn't surrendered.
Therefore, the planet
we see ahead
still belongs to the enemy.
At least, that's
the official position.
They still haven't surrendered?
Yes, that's correct.
[NEREIS]
I find that rather surprising.
[NEFEE] What I find surprising
is that you didn't
already know that, Nereis.
After all, you are
the supreme commander
of the defense fleet
in this region.
[NEREIS]
Well, yes.
But what I also didn't realize
was how the government
of those Landers would affect
the outcome of our battle.
Hold on a minute.
If they haven't surrendered,
what are we defending?
Surely we're not defending
the planet from their own side?
I always said you had a severe
lack of common sense...
What we're defending
is the Aptic Gate.
It's obvious, isn't it?
Of course I knew that!
So if they haven't surrendered,
and we acquired water
from their planet,
we'd effectively be pillaging.
Pillaging...
I wonder how long
it's been since
anyone in the Star Forces
did some of that?
You're not seriously
thinking of it, are you?
[NEREIS]
Why not?
Don't you think it's got a bit
of an artistic flair to it?
[NEFEE]
No, I don't.
[NEREIS] It would also solve
a very real problem for us.
We're running out of coolant.
If we want to win,
we're going to need
water from somewhere.
You do have a point there.
The most important
thing is that we win.
[NEREIS] There you are then!
We should go pillage!
All right--the end
justifies the means!
Let's go get some water!
And how are we gonna do that?
[NEREIS, NEFEE]
Hm?
To reach the ocean on Aptic III
we'd have to enter
the atmosphere.
Which is no mean feat!
It'd be easier to
contact headquarters
and get supplies of
water transported here
through Plane Space.
[NEREIS] But if we did that,
we'd run out again in no time!
[OFFICER 8B] We'd run out if it
came from the planet, too.
[OFFICER 8A]
I think she's right.
I'm happy to calculate
how much coolant
we can get from the planet
versus receiving supplies
direct from headquarters,
if that would help you
decide what to do.
[NEREIS]
No need to go to that trouble.
Must we go below
the planet's atmosphere
to do this? There's no other
way to get their water?
For instance,
couldn't we collect it
from the air instead
of the ocean?
[OFFICER 8A] Our fleet
doesn't have the equipment
that's needed to undertake
such an operation.
In time, we might be able
to make some progress
with the materials
we already have on board,
but I think it's unlikely
we'd succeed in time
for the battle.
How long do you think
you need to do this?
Approximately one year.
All right, that's too long.
We'll just have
to manage without.
I should've guessed that
there'd be a good reason
why the Star Forces
didn't go around
pillaging planets nowadays.
It's just not worth the effort!
It's a bit of a shame, isn't it?
Something that's right
in front of our noses
and we can't reach it.
[NEFEE]
Hm?
Such an experience isn't
entirely unfamiliar to you.
[laughs]
Not as much as it is to you.
Sometimes, you don't know
what's in front of you
unless you reach for it.
[NEREIS]
Anyway...
Back to the conference
on the battle plan!
I'd like to present
you with my thoughts.
And would value your feedback.
[NEREIS] These are the
mobile space-time mines.
We will remove them from
the battleships in advance
and set their targets.
Of course, we'll do the
same for the backup mines
carried by the transport ships.
Here we see the placement
of the attack ships
and the guard ships.
Additionally, we will
have patrol ships
in the outer regions.
We plan to position
the flagship here.
And these are the
front-line ships.
[NEFEE]
Considering this is your idea,
it's a fairly
impressive formation.
Simple but effective.
Thank you, Brother.
Now I'd like to explain
the battle process.
Just before the enemy
enters regular space,
we'll send all our mines
into Plane Space.
After placing and detonating
all their mines,
the front-line battle
ships would normally
have served their purpose
and would therefore retreat.
However, since we
have a limited supply
of coolant, we can leave these
ships in their positions
and re-assign them
as supply ships.
The rest is up to
the attack ships
and the patrol ships.
As soon as the enemy appears,
we'll strike them with
an all-out attack.
We just need to
make sure they never
enter regular space. That is
my strategy for the battle.
I think this is the
most logical approach
and the one that will cause
the least number of casualties.
The main fleet will arrive here
within 72 hours at the most.
We have to hold out until then.
Anyone have any questions?
I don't think so.
You know, this is
a very simple plan
and I think it might work.
Yes! It's excellent!
No sign of the usual Bebaus
Spectacular Insanity! [gasps]
[NEFEE] I can work out
all the details myself.
You carry on and do
whatever it is you do
as the commanding admiral.
You're saying I'm in your way?
Well, yes.
I have to admit you did
come up with a good plan.
We don't want you doing
anything to spoil it now,
so you might as well go
and do your paperwork.
[NEREIS growls]
What a feeble excuse
to get me out the way.
Sometimes I wonder
why I ever became a
commander in the first place.
I hate this thing.
You're not really the type
to be a chief of staff, Nereis.
[NEREIS]
The same goes for you, Nefee.
The only difference
between you and me
is that your personality
is not suited to being
a chief of staff
or a commander.
[NEREIS]
Hmph.
[BEIKAL]
Hello, Your Highness.
[LAFIEL]
I'm just your unit commander,
so I'd appreciate it
if you'd stop calling me
"Your Highness."
[BEIKAL]
But why?
Knights such as myself
don't often get the chance
to speak directly with
royalty. It's an honor.
In that case, do as you wish.
Things were pretty rough
for you the other day.
[LAFIEL] It's amazing that
we made it back alive.
We were very lucky.
[BEIKAL] On the contrary,
I heard it was all due
to your outstanding
performance.
Your reputation proceeds you.
You're just as good as I am.
With all the experience
you've had,
I'm sure no one has any
doubt about your abilities.
Well, I suppose you
could be right.
[LAFIEL]
Come on now, or you'll be late.
Yeah!
Getting an invitation from
an Imperial princess!
This is a once in
a lifetime experience!
Steady, boy--that's not a mouse!
You know, whenever I bring
Diaho up to the bridge with me,
Samson gets kind of
annoyed about it.
Have you got any
idea why that is?
He says he doesn't want any cat
hairs getting in the equipment.
Convenient excuse.
Human hairs are just as bad.
The machines have been
designed to withstand
that sort of thing.
[JINTO]
I know.
But I think there's more
to it than that for Samson.
He takes pride in looking
after the equipment.
He feels responsible
and his pride means
that he doesn't want
anything around that might
potentially damage
the machinery.
Samson's pride or my enjoyment.
It's obvious which one's
more important to you.
In that case, why don't
you talk to him?
Try and persuade him that Diaho
should be allowed up here.
Sure, if he asks me.
[sighs]
[EKURYUA]
Jinto...
Huh?
How old is Diaho?
Umm... Uh...
I think he's four years old.
I see.
And can you tell me
how old you are?
I was 16 when I got him,
so that makes me 20.
Is there anything else?
What does it feel like
for you to get old?
[laughs]
[JINTO] The Abh sure don't
beat around the bush!
Couldn't tell you--
I'm still young!
Humans don't start to
show any signs of aging
until we're a lot older!
Oh, okay.
I'll just ask the Line
Wing Aviator instead.
I don't think that's
a very good idea.
I'm not sure he'd take
it such good spirits--
he can be a little sensitive
about stuff like that!
[SOBAASH]
You're having a drink?
Hey there, Senior Aviator!
I'm not gonna be
able to have a drink
for quite a while.
So I thought I'd stock up!
[SOBAASH]
That's gotta be bad for you.
So, are you gonna
offer me one or not?
Huh? But you just said
it was bad for ya!
Do you have a problem with that?
Sometimes the bad things
in life are the most fun.
Ha, ha. I'll have
to remember that!
Thanks. Fill her up.
So I heard that purebred
Abhs can't get drunk
no matter how much
they drink. Is that true?
It does affect us a little bit.
But we can't get
completely drunk--
it's just not
possible genetically.
Now, if we were to inject
the alcohol straight
into our bloodstream,
that'd be a different story.
Here's to genetic engineering!
You know, if I wasn't
able to get drunk,
it would be like a curse.
Sometimes you want
to forget things.
Sometimes you need to forget.
[SOBAASH] When we feel
like that we take a pill
which helps us to sleep.
[SAMSON]
Well, I guess that's healthier.
[SOBAASH]
The Abh are a healthy race.
[SAMSON]
That's not what most of humanity
thinks about you.
[SOBAASH] We can't always live
up to their expectations.
An Abh who's worried about
what other people
think of them?!
I've never heard
of such a thing!
To tell you the truth,
I don't really care
what other people think.
But on the other hand,
we're not going to
deny what they say.
Incidentally, I don't
think I've ever seen you
be this open with me.
That might be because
the Senior Aviator
hasn't ever seen
me when I'm drunk.
[laughs] I'm positive
I've seen you drunk before.
It's possible you've
seen me drinkin'.
But never drunk.
Is that so?
And I'm meant to believe
you're drunk now?
[SAMSON] Heh. Well, this is my
second bottle, after all.
Do you regularly drink
as much as this?
[SAMSON]
No, no, no!
This is a luxury I allow myself
maybe once or twice a year.
Normally, I just get
a little bit tipsy.
Then why allow yourself
the luxury today?
What's going on?
[SAMSON]
Hm...
Very soon, we are
going to be attacked
by an enemy ten
times our size.
That sort of event doesn't
tend to happen very often
in your lifetime.
Well, yes.
If it was something
that happened often,
then there probably wouldn't
be much of a lifetime
left to live.
[SAMSON]
Exactly.
Tell you what--
once we get through
this next battle, I'll buy you
a bottle of your favorite booze.
Huh? That's generous of you.
But I did hear that
the senior aviator
was wealthy, so I'll
accept your offer!
I have to say,
that rumor's a bit
of an exaggeration!
But I think I can
afford a few drinks!
[SAMSON]
Hm.
I've never been so happy
to pour my alcohol
into someone else's glass!
[ATOSURYUA]
There are no reinforcements.
But that was to be expected.
This is our position here.
Our mission here
is straightforward.
We are charged with the task
of destroying the enemy.
It's as simple as that.
[BEIKAL]
Yes, it sounds simple enough.
But how long do we envision
the battle lasting?
We haven't got the resources
to keep attacking
every enemy ship that
shows up in our region
of the battlefield.
A maximum of 72 hours.
That's what the
defensive command
has warned us to expect.
Of course nothing's certain
about this, but we'll just
have to take their word for it.
I'm afraid I can't provide
any more information.
After all, I'm merely
an Assault Unit Commander.
Any other questions?
[gasps]
[ATOSURYUA]
Very well.
We will have lost this
battle if we let the enemy
enter through the gate.
Therefore, we must defend it
without concern for
the loss of life.
You may consider
this to be reckless.
To be honest, it is reckless
and I have to admit,
I am concerned about you all.
Some of you may eventually
go on to become admirals
and take command of a fleet.
If that ever happens to you,
I want you to never forget
what you feel like
right here and now.
I get the impression
you don't aspire
to become an admiral
of the fleet.
Am I right, Commander?
Me? No way!
To be perfectly honest
with you, Captain,
just being in charge of a unit
in a desolate part of
the universe like this
is stressful enough.
No, I don't want to
command a whole fleet.
The difference
between royalty
and nobility like myself is
that we can be selfish.
Another difference...
...is that for royalty, the
territories are nothing more
than an amusement
to pass the time.
However...
...for us in the nobility,
the territories are our life.
[LAFIEL] I can't be sure,
but I think she was aiming
that comment specifically at me.
[SAMSON]
Time to change the subject.
So, my senior aviator friend,
what do you think
of the captain?
[SOBAASH]
What do you mean?
[SAMSON] Well it seems
strange. You know...
I mean, she's the captain
and she's only 19!
[SOBAASH] I don't think that's
too young to be the captain
of an attack ship.
One of the most important
qualities you need
is sharp reflexes, which are
better when you're young.
[SAMSON] No, no, no.
I haven't got any doubts
about her abilities.
It's just that...
Well, I've been workin'
for the Star Forces
for 20 years now!
Makes you think, doesn't it?
When I started to
work for these guys,
the captain hadn't
even been born yet!
[SOBAASH]
I'm sorry, but you've lost me.
I can't figure out what
your problem is here.
[SAMSON]
What?
I don't know.
It's the drink talkin'.
If you really want my
opinion on the captain,
I have a theory you
might be interested in.
[SAMSON]
Oh?
[SOBAASH] Frankly, I'm
a little disappointed.
You must know there
are a lot of stories
about the Abriel family.
Given those, I'd say
the captain's personality
is a bit too calm.
[SAMSON coughs]
You seriously think she's calm?!
[SOBAASH] Far more than
I thought she would be.
Maybe she's having a hard
time settling down,
feels a bit out of place.
And I expect she's
finding it difficult
to get used to her superiors
ordering her around,
given her privileged
background as a member
of the royal family with
everyone waiting on her
hand and foot the whole time.
Feels a bit out of place here.
I remember some kid
sayin' something
along those lines.
[SAMSON laughs] Hey!
Maybe that's my problem, too!
I'm just feelin' out of place.
When I was a regular
crew member
everyone around me
was ordinary
and regular like me:
old, young, men, women,
all types of people.
But up there on the bridge,
all I see is young Abhs
like you all the time.
I mean, you're
actually older than me
but you still look
like a young lad--
Sorry, I meant to say lass--
just a slip of the tongue!
Well, I guess...
...there is another
Lander around.
He's a nice kid.
But he's no more than a boy
and even he's a nobleman.
It's just like...
[SAMSON speaking Baronh]
[SAMSON]
Sorry...
[SOBAASH laughs] That's okay.
It doesn't bother me.
However, I don't think
I can say much in reply.
[ATOSURYUA] We've only
drunk half the bottle.
I intend to save the other
half until after the battle.
Unless all five of you
are here to enjoy it.
No one will drink it.
Here's to your safe
return! A toast!
There's a lot to do before
the battle commences.
The ceremony's over. Dismissed!
Line Wing Aviator...?
If you're going to go to sleep,
you should really sleep
in your own room.
[CREW 9A]
Close the hatches!
[CREW 9B]
Hatches closed!
[CREW 9A] Prepare to dismantle
pathway connectors
and store them!
[CREW 9B]
Preparations complete!
[CREW 9A]
Engage the Stabilization Device.
[CREW 9C]
Engaged!
[CREW 9A]
Dismantle pathway connectors!
[CREW 9C]
Connectors dismantling!
[CREW 9D]
All ships fully operational.
[CREW 9B] Preparations
for departure complete!
[CREW 9C] The Stabilization
Control Device is ready.
[CREW 9A]
Turn on the main engine!
[COMMUNICATIONS OFFICER 9A]
I repeat. The enemy fleet
will enter combat
range within six hours.
Prepare for departure.
[LAFIEL]
Daisiele!