[JINTO]
We had been assigned to
the Battleship
Squadron Latouche
as part of the First Division
of the 1058th Battalion.
[JINTO] Our mission was
to patrol the regions
of the Aptic System
which had been conquered
by Admiral Spoor.
[JINTO] Our assault ships are
small, but versatile craft
whose main weapons are
anti-proton cannons.
Unfortunately, the defense
shields are weak,
so we have to travel
in units of six ships.
After three months, the
Aptic System seemed like
our very own backup base.
[CREW 3A] We'll be arriving
in the Aptic System shortly.
[JINTO] Operation Phantom
Flame seems to be going
without a hitch. In fact,
it's going so well,
that our leaders are worried
that something isn't right.
[JINTO]
However, our captain,
Abriel Nei Dubrusk
Paryunu Lafiel,
differs from the other leaders
because she is worrying
about something else entirely.
[JINTO]
About this.
Captain!
There's a message
from the commander.
Huh?
Put her on screen.
I would like to confirm that
today's joint training session
is now over.
All ships are to return to
Dakul moving at regular speed.
Understood, thank you.
[JINTO] Hecto-Commander
Atosuryua was Lafiel's
superior officer as
commander of our Battalion.
They had a very
unique connection,
but it wasn't
necessarily a good one.
Three years earlier, Lafiel
had killed Baron Febdash,
who was the commander's
older brother.
[NARRATOR speaking Baronh]
[JINTO]
I wonder what she thinks of us?
[LAFIEL]
Does it really worry you?
[JINTO]
No, not really, but...
[LAFIEL] Come on,
tell the truth. That face!
You look like a child
who's done something wrong!
[JINTO] Cut it out! How come
it doesn't bother you?
[LAFIEL] How many times
do I have to tell you?
I had no choice--there was
nothing else I could've done.
[JINTO] Yeah, but the
hecto-commander might still
hold some sort of
grudge against us.
[JINTO] Lafiel got this
worried look on her face,
but then quickly came
up with a response
that told me we weren't gonna
talk about it anymore.
Jinto, it's a waste of time
even thinking about it.
[sighs] I wish I could
persuade her otherwise.
[EKURYUA] Captain.
May I have a word with you?
[LAFIEL]
What is it?
It's about this little one.
[LAFIEL] It's just one
problem after another.
So you've decided that you want
to keep him on board as well?
[EKURYUA] Well, I compared
the probable fatality rates
between keeping him
on board the Basroil
and sending him
back to Lakfakalle.
And what did you find?
[EKURYUA]
Before I give you my conclusion,
I've prepared an
explanatory presentation.
It doesn't look like I've got
any choice in the matter.
[sighs]
[TALAS] You mean you're
not going to issue
a summons demanding
our surrender?!
[DUSANYU]
That's correct.
We have no such plans
at the moment.
Besides, even if you were
to surrender right now,
we wouldn't gain much by it,
so there's not really any point.
[TALAS] Hmph! So all
that's going to happen
is that our planet will be
subject to a blockade?
[DUSANYU]
That's the intention.
The blockade will be
reinforced from ground level
to a height of 300 wesdaj
above the planet.
You will be able to move
freely within that area,
but if anyone makes an incursion
into the no-fly zone,
they will be stopped
and any aggressive action will
be dealt with accordingly.
But that's terrible.
Our planet is not
self-sufficient--we depend
on imports of food for survival.
If you impose a blockade
like this, people will starve!
[DUSANYU] We have no desire
to harm your society
by our actions.
The fact that we
are not actively
demanding your surrender
doesn't stop you
from surrendering
of your own accord.
We intend is to remain
in this region
for quite some time
so you are at liberty
to choose to surrender
at any time
you consider convenient.
What I don't understand
is why you would
go to all this trouble.
When our intelligence
reports suggest
that you don't have any
interest in our planet at all.
[DUSANYU] To be frank with you,
this is correct. We don't.
However, what we are interested
in is the nearby Sord
and the hydrogen and water
resources to be found
in the Fourth Aptic System.
[TALAS] Are you deliberately
trying to insult me?
[DUSANYU]
Certainly not, Mr. President,
I was merely trying
to be honest.
[TALAS] You dismiss the
importance of our planet--
how could I not be insulted?
[DUSANYU]
I'm sorry to hear that.
How about a compromise?
We will demand your
surrender, but only under
the following conditions:
One, if our operations
are settling down nicely,
two, if we are
still successfully
barricading the
planet and three,
if you haven't
already surrendered.
[TALAS] Well, that's
something, I suppose.
I have to say, I feel
a little relieved.
[DUSANYU] Of course,
we realize that our actions
have the potential to cause
the people on your planet
to fall into a state
of unrest and anarchy.
Having to deal with such a
situation would be an unwelcome,
unnecessary and
onerous task for us.
Therefore, I suggest you
consider surrendering before
things get out of hand.
[TALAS] I don't want
anarchy on this planet
any more than you do.
And with respect, if there
was, we wouldn't want
outsiders such as yourselves
dealing with it,
even if you were
indirectly to blame.
In any case, this was a useful
discussion, Your Highness.
At least we now understand
each other's position.
I'm sure we can discuss
the finer details
amongst ourselves
at another time.
[DUSANYU] Mm. Thank you and
good night, Mr President, sir.
[TALAS]
Huh?
[DUSANYU]
Hmph.
Aptic. Mystel. Dalmav.
Wimpel. Miofrantia.
We've come so far,
so quickly, so easily.
All defeated without
lifting a finger in battle.
I suspect the enemy is
gathering their forces
elsewhere in space.
Somewhere out there...
It all looks so peaceful.
So, how come you didn't demand
his immediate surrender?
Remember that, in times of war,
the situation is
constantly shifting.
You never know, the United
Mankind might recapture
this system at any time.
And, if that happens,
the president,
who is so keen on surrendering
his planet to us,
wouldn't be in a very
good position, would he?
How very generous.
I think the real
reason was because
you didn't want
to do the paperwork
involved in drawing up a treaty.
The president was ready
for you to dictate
the terms of his
surrender to him.
And you ignored him completely.
What an excellent
commander-in-chief you are,
Your Highness. Always
managing to give people
what they don't want, and at
the same time not giving them
what they do want.
[DUSANYU] I prefer to describe
it as a guiltless pleasure.
[KENESH]
I didn't mean to criticize.
If I didn't know you better,
I'd say that your
behavior was verging
on being described
as incorrigible.
Oh, really?
And I have no doubt
that there will be
any number of times in the
future to reconfirm that,
given your track record.
Ah... There will be
no need to reconfirm
"any number of times."
Highness, I'm not he
one who needs to.
By that, I hope you're
not suggesting
that I'm the one
who needs to do so?
[DUSANYU] We really must
keep this a secret, Chief.
Keep what a secret?
[DUSANYU] The fact that
the commander-in-chief
and his chief of staff
don't get along very well.
It might promote
dissention in the ranks.
I doubt you have anything
to worry about.
I think we manage to
get along just fine.
It's hard to believe
we're in the middle
of a battlefield the way
everyone's enjoying themselves.
[ATOSURYUA] You're Supply
Officer Lin, aren't you?
[JINTO]
Huh?
H-Hecto-Commander Atosuryua!
Nice to meet you.
My father told me all about you.
Really? I liked your dad.
He was always really kind to me.
[ATOSURYUA]
Relax a little!
If you're worried
about the situation
with my brother,
please don't be.
[JINTO sighs]
Are you sure it's okay?
[ATOSURYUA]
Well, my brother being murdered
isn't open for discussion.
But it's hardly what you'd
call a good experience.
Well, yes, I can
certainly see that.
To tell you the truth,
my brother and I
had our differences.
For instance, we didn't always
see eye to eye over my father.
He wanted to keep him
confined as a prisoner.
I didn't agree with that.
As you might've guessed,
we weren't very close.
[JINTO]
Er... Well, I see...
I-I don't know what to say.
But I am sorry
about your brother.
[ATOSURYUA]
Thanks. It was a shame he died.
The problem now is what
to do with his title.
[JINTO]
What?
That's great, thanks.
[JINTO]
What do you mean "his title"?
He was the Baron of Febdash,
which is in the
middle of nowhere.
I never liked the place--
not when I was a child
and certainly not now.
Really?
[ATOSURYUA]
I was relieved when my brother
inherited the title and not me.
It meant I didn't
have to live there.
[ATOSURYUA] I wanted to
stay and enjoy myself
in Lakfakalle for
the rest of my life.
But then that princess
of yours showed up
and ruined everything.
No more easy life for me!
My princess? I'm sorry,
but if you're talking about who
I think you're talking about,
then she's not my princess.
She's the captain of our ship,
and that's how we address her.
Don't get touchy!
It was just a
stupid expression--
I didn't mean anything by it!
I see.
I thought that maybe
you were holding
some sort of grudge against her.
You know, from what my
father told me about you,
I got the impression
you were a smart kid,
but I don't see any
evidence of it right now!
Sorry if I offended you.
Even if I did hold a grudge,
why would I bother wasting
my time mentioning it to you?
It would be far
easier to make use
of my rank and position
to get my revenge on her.
I'd sit tight and wait
for the right opportunity.
A grudge? Hah!
I see, but...
I thought you didn't
want your title.
[laughs] It's no big
deal to me, you know!
Having said that, being the head
of a noble family isn't so bad.
The big house that comes
with being Baroness Febdash
could be nice to live
in with a few renovations
here and there.
I could even take a leaf
out of my brother's book
and surround myself with
lots of handsome young men.
Anyway, there's no point
thinking about this
until the war's over.
Well, I suppose... that's
a good way to look at it.
Anyway.
Tell that princess of yours or
captain--or whatever she is--
that I don't bear
a grudge against her.
What happened, happened,
life goes on,
and we should just
forget about it.
I don't understand.
Why don't you tell her yourself?
[ATOSURYUA]
It's... difficult.
[JINTO]
"Difficult"? Why?
[ATOSURYUA]
She's an Abriel princess, right?
It's fine talking business
with her, but as soon as
you wanna talk about anything
personal or private...
Well, she doesn't exactly
make it easy for you.
Is that so?
[JINTO]
Aw... It's not fair!
Why do I always have
to be the go-between?
Just because I seem to
get along with everyone,
they assume I can do
the talking for them.
It's not fair!
Don't forget to tell
her what I said.
[JINTO]
I won't.
[alarm blares]
[CREW 3B] Six unidentified
space-time bubbles
are heading towards us.
They appear to have
come from the direction
of Wimpel and are presumed
to be enemy scout ships.
All staff return to your
stations immediately.
Ugh, this is serious!
We're going to have to
talk about this later!
This is more urgent.
Everyone needs to rendezvous
in 12 minutes and 37 seconds!
[LAFIEL] Hm. Attention!
This is the captain speaking!
All off-duty crew,
you have ten minutes
to proceed to your stations!
I repeat.
Off-duty crew,
you have ten minutes
to proceed to your stations!
[JINTO] We're not in training
anymore--this is the real thing!
Everyone in the blue category
is now prepared and
ready for action!
Understood!
Euch, yuck! Tastes disgusting!
There's nothin' worse
than having to work
when you feel like this!
Hey, Jinto! You're late!
Sorry.
I mean, excuse me, Captain!
[LAFIEL]
Okay. Close the hatches!
I want all connecting
passageways to be separated
and shut down!
All connecting
passageways to be separated
and shut down!
Passageway separation complete!
[LAFIEL] Activate the
forward thrust engines
with minimum propulsion!
Engines activated!
[LAFIEL]
And we're off!
[ATOSURYUA]
This is command speaking.
We now have our official orders.
We are to seize the unidentified
space-time bubbles.
If we identify them
as enemy craft,
we are to eliminate them.
I'll send you the
files containing
the location of our rendezvous.
All ships must try to arrive
there as soon as possible.
Any questions?
Very well.
We have a number of crew
members on this mission
for whom this will be
their first battle!
To be honest, this is
my first time as well.
Hmph! I have no idea
what that squadron
was doing in Wimpel.
I guess you can't
expect too much
from an advance force.
But their mistakes
are not the issue here.
However you look at it,
the enemy has managed
to outwit us,
and you have to give them
credit for this maneuver.
Salute the courage of the enemy!
We have received the
location of the rendezvous.
I'll forward the information
to your terminal.
Activate the main engines!
[SAMSON]
Main engines activated!
Huh?
Diaho? What are you doing here?!
Let's see who arrives first!
Stay there and you'd
better keep quiet!
Huh?!
Captain!
There's a message from
another ship, the Ryumusof .
They say our actions are
violating safety protocol!
[LAFIEL]
Hm?
They're insisting
they have to speak
directly with you, Captain!
Tell them I'm too busy!
Tell them I can't
talk right now!
Besides, ships like the Ryumusof
probably won't be
fighting in the battle.
They don't seem very pleased.
[LAFIEL]
Senior Aviator!
Are there any ships from
our squadron ahead of us?
[SOBAASH]
Yes, Captain, there's one.
[LAFIEL]
Which one?
The squadron's lead
assault ship, the Gamroil .
[LAFIEL]
Distance?
Approximately two sedaj.
It looks like
Hecto-Commander Atosuryua
will have the honor
of arriving first.
We've been put on standby.
We're also receiving
debriefing information.
I'll display it on
the monitor now.
[LAFIEL] The yellow symbols
show the space-time bubbles,
which are possible enemy ships?
[SOBAASH] From their mass,
I'd say they're probably
patrol ships. Their objective
is presumably to scout the area
around Wimpel and the Aptic
System in an attempt
to estimate the strength
of our forces.
[LAFIEL]
They're very close.
If we make the decision
to act aggressively,
it's possible we could force
them to abort their mission.
Well, that's fine with me.
Let's get this
over with quickly.
The sooner we finish this,
the sooner I can be in the bar.
I can just see it--my favorite
bottle waiting for me...
I didn't get much of a
chance to drink it earlier.
All this talk of yours
is making me thirsty!
Whaddya say we get a drink?
We're only on standby
so we've got time
before we have to move--
Jinto, instead of
worrying about drinks,
worry about this cat of yours.
[EKURYUA] There he goes again,
getting himself into trouble.
If you're getting drinks,
I'll have a Teal Nom.
You like it hot with Lope
floating in it, don't you?
Coming up, Captain!
[EKURYUA] And I'd like
a SoyAsa, a cold one.
What? Don't you
wanna stay with me?
[DIAHO growls]
Well...
He is my cat, after all!
What? Are you jealous?
I want my drink cold,
with apple flavoring.
You got it.
[SAMSON]
Captain!
Request permission for me to get
something stronger from the bar.
[LAFIEL]
I presume that was a joke.
Sorry, I gotta put you in here.
It'll just be
for a little while.
[SAMSON] I was just trying
to lighten up the mood here!
Come on, humor me!
You could at least pretend
that it was funny!
I don't want anything
to drink, my boy.
Okay, but next time
don't call me "my boy"!
Get rid of that cat
and get involved
with some proper
adult relationships,
then I'll stop calling
you "my boy."
In that case, just
call me "my boy."
While you're there,
I'll have a SoyAsa, too.
There should be some
leaves down there
from the Yoni Kingdom.
And make it with
lots of sugar, please.
[JINTO]
Coming right up!
[ATOSURYUA] We have received
our next orders.
All ships in the squadron
are to enter Plane Space.
After entering,
assemble behind my ship
as quickly as possible in
a single column formation.
The space-time
bubbles have been
positively identified
as enemy ships.
Our mission is
to eliminate them.
If we let even a single
one of them get away,
we will have failed.
As this is our first battle,
we must make a good impression.
We have to succeed,
do you understand?
Any questions, anyone?
Very well then.
I'll see you once
we're in Plane Space.
Let's go!
[LAFIEL]
Chief Engineer!
Prepare to generate
space-time bubble!
[SAMSON]
Yes, Captain!
Entering the Sord in 30 seconds!
It's time to activate
the space-time bubble!
[SAMSON]
Space time bubble activated!
We're now prepared
to enter Plane Space!
[SOBAASH]
Five...
Four...
Three...
Two...
One...
We're in! We've
entered Plane Space!
Check immediately where
the lead assault ship
Gamroil is situated.
It's 500 wesdaj ahead!
[LAFIEL]
Follow them!
Roger!
Receiving a transmission
from the Gamroil .
We're to perform
space-time fusion.
[SOBAASH]
In five seconds...
Three...
Two...
One.
[meows]
[ATOSURYUA] You can all see
the situation we're facing.
I don't need to explain it.
For now, let's just
try and avoid
getting ourselves into trouble.
Prepare to fire the
anti-proton cannon!
[SOBAASH] Releasing the
safety devices for numbers
one to four now!
[JINTO] As stipulated by
Operation Phantom Flame
we have passed through the
United Mankind territories
in a bid to link our territories
and divide theirs in two.
In doing so, the
Star Forces have conquered
and acquired many Sords
and planet systems.
The First Fleet,
commanded by Admiral Spoor
had led the way and,
even as we speak,
we're expanding our territory.
[JINTO] Although the Third
Aptic System that we conquered
seems distant from the front
line of battle in terms of
regular space, so long
as there are Sords,
which are the gateways
into Plane Space,
we cannot give up the
possibility of enemy attack.
Therefore, as long
as the Sords exist,
that's the front line of battle.
[SOBAASH]
Space-time fusion!
All ships! Attack!
[JINTO]
Our battle has now begun.
Well, maybe...
That's not it at all!
It's that we all survived
the test of our first battle!
Continue with space-time fusion!
Roger.
[grunts]
[GAMROIL'S 2nd OFFICER]
We've just had confirmation
that the Helzroil
has been destroyed.
They must have
retreated too late!
I can't believe there are
casualties in my squadron!
We're being attacked!
[JINTO]
Lafiel!
It's going to be a direct hit!
[gasps]
The anti-proton cannon!