[CREW chattering Baronh]
[speaking Baronh]
[CREW 1A speaking Baronh]
[CREW 1E speaking Baronh]
[speaking Baronh]
[SPOOR speaking Baronh]
[NARRATOR speaking Baronh]
[SOBAASH]
Space-time fusion in...
...10...
...9, 8, 7, 6,
5, 4,
3, 2, 1...
Entering Plane Space!
[LAFIEL gasps]
Get ready!
[LAFIEL grunts]
Somehow, the enemy target
managed to dodge our fire!
In that case, maneuver
under its wings!
Laser cannons!
Fire at full power!
Roger! Firing!
Good work! Now turn the
ship around 180 degrees!
Prepare to fire the
anti-proton cannon.
[gasps]
[LAFIEL]
They're fast!
[CREW grunting]
[grunts] The anti-proton
cannon's taken a direct hit!
We're losing power--
0.9, 0.8,
0.7, and it's still dropping!
The loss of power
has caused a failure
in the defensive
magnetic shield.
[JINTO] We're losing
atmosphere in Sector 7!
The atmospheric pressure's
down to 0.63.
There are no signs of life
from the crew members there!
We've gotta shut
down the sector!
Lockdown complete!
Sector 7 has been sealed!
That should stop the problem
affecting other sectors.
We can only hope so!
Start the space-time diffusion!
Hurry!
It's no good!
We're not going to make it!
[CREW grunts]
[COMPUTER VOICE 1A]
The ship has been destroyed.
[sighs] Any clues yet
as to why it went wrong?
No, nothing yet.
At least, I can't see
anything obvious.
[SAMSON] We should
continue investigating.
[LAFIEL]
Very well. Carry on.
Captain, transmission
coming in for you.
[LAFIEL]
Put it on screen.
That wasn't bad,
Deca-Commander Abriel.
Although, you
sometimes sacrifice
efficiency for...
a certain artistic flair.
However, I think that,
with a little bit of luck,
you should be able to survive.
I would like to wish you and
your crew members all the best.
And now it's time to end
the battle simulation.
--[SOBAASH] Captain?
--[LAFIEL] Hm?
[LAFIEL]
Finish up here for me please.
I'm going to lie down.
Get some rest.
The simulation took
a lot out of her.
[JINTO]
We lived on a well-known ship.
But it wasn't well-known
because it had been
in a famous battle or anything.
Its fame came from being home
to two members of royalty.
One of them was our captain,
Deca-Commander Abriel.
She was a princess of
one of the royal families
of the Humankind Empire Abh.
The other was me, Count Jinto
of the Lin Syune
Rocke Hyde Family.
I'm a nobleman.
However, this ship
was the only place
I had to call home.
And, if truth be told,
it was the only place
where I felt like
I really belonged.
Why are you looking at me?
Is something wrong?
[sighs] So, Navigator
Sobaash, do you think
the time has come to tell
him what we need him to do?
He's still very young--
do you think he can cope?
[SOBAASH] Well, as
vice-captain of this ship,
I could order him to do it,
but forcing someone
to do such a dangerous
task doesn't feel right.
How about you try some
gentle persuasion?
I'll give it a go.
So, young Secretary
Jinto, listen up.
Yes?
During that battle simulation,
the captain didn't perform
as well as expected
and her pride was
damaged quite badly.
Do ya see what I'm getting at?
[JINTO] I think you're being
unfair if you're insinuating
that the captain
isn't up to the job.
You've gotta remember that
Hecto-Commander Kotokeil
has way more experience
than the captain--I mean,
she's only just taken
command of this ship
and can't be expected
to know everything from...
[SAMSON] Yes, Your Highness,
I'm fully aware of that.
I'd prefer it if you didn't
address me that way.
[sighs] Fine, Secretary Lin.
Don't misunderstand me--
none of us have a problem
fighting under the
captain's command.
However, you have to admit that
she's got a lot to learn,
and inexperience can be
dangerous in a battle situation.
[SAMSON] Even if we
join forces with other,
more experienced
captains in the fleet,
we'll still be under
the captain's command.
That said, we sincerely
believe that she has
great potential and we
want her to succeed.
Are you following
what I'm saying so far?
Yes.
[SAMSON] We have to make sure
the captain is feeling
positive about her
ability and gets herself
in the right frame
of mind to fight.
If we can do that,
then we all have a better
chance of getting
out of this alive.
At least we don't have to worry
about her being overconfident,
which can sometimes
be more dangerous.
[JINTO]
"Dangerous"?
She's just feelin' a bit down
in the dumps, that's all!
[SAMSON] Well, maybe dangerous
is too strong a word.
But a lot of fighting
is about psychology
and you need to
believe in yourself.
So our chances of success
would be improved
if our captain believed
we could win.
It's pretty straightforward,
don't you think?
Guess so.
And this is where you
come in to the picture
to help us out!
What do you mean where
I come in to the picture?
What do you want me to do?
Come on, do I really
need to tell ya that?
You want me to go in
and cheer her up--
boost her confidence?
Give her a bit of pep talk?
You got it--you're definitely
the best man for the job.
Now I'm the one with
no self-confidence.
[SAMSON] I'm not expecting
you to work miracles here!
Just spend some time
chatting with her.
Give her a chance to
let off a little steam.
[JINTO]
Her? Let off steam?
Um... Well, maybe you're right.
I guess she's not the type to do
that in front of other people.
After all, she is an Abriel.
But the fact remains
that she's feeling
a bit low and I think we should
give her a chance to talk.
Don't you think
it's a good idea?
Well, sure, yeah.
But why can't you do it?
Do I have to tell you that?
Isn't it obvious?
Listen, if the captain
was in a really foul mood,
what would you do?
[JINTO] Well, I'd try to
calm her down, of course.
How about you, Sobaash?
What would you do
in that situation?
I'd run in the other direction!
You know, suddenly remember
some urgent business.
You see that?
That's what most of us would do
if we were faced
with an angry Abriel.
Run away! But you're different!
You said you'd try
and calm her down.
Oh...
Are you sure you're not
reading too much into this?
The captain's perfectly capable
of taking care of herself.
Besides, if she knew we were
talking about her like this,
it would really make her mad!
[SAMSON] I think I'd prefer
to see an angry Abriel
than a depressed one.
Seems more natural.
At least we know
how to deal with it!
I suppose you've
got a point there.
Although...
I'm not sure that her
being angry is any better
for her than being
down in the dumps.
It might seem more natural
for her to be angry,
but it doesn't mean it's
a good thing, does it?
Of course not.
[JINTO] I've known her for
years and years, right?
Well, one thing I've
noticed is that what annoys
the captain more
than anything else
is when people treat
her like a child.
If she ever found out
that we've been trying
to "take care of her,"
then even I wouldn't wanna
be around to suffer
the consequences.
[SAMSON] Hm. You've got one
up on us--you certainly
know her better than we do.
[SAMSON] We're just the
crew she's been allocated,
but you... you're friends!
Over the years, you've shared
adventures with her,
she gives you little presents--
you're even allowed
to call her by her real name!
[JINTO] Huh? How did
you know about that?
You haven't exactly
been hiding it.
I've heard you use
her name three times.
Uh--
[SAMSON] No need to be
embarrassed, Secretary Lin.
Just because you and
the captain are friends
doesn't mean we're gonna
treat you any differently.
You're part of the team on board
this ship just like us.
We all have our jobs to do
and we do them well--
there's no reason for
us to be jealous of you
being friends with her.
[chuckles] That wasn't what
I was worried about.
[SAMSON] In that case,
there's nothing to stop you
from going to talk to the
captain to see what's up.
'Kay...
Let's just hold on
a minute here!
I think you're reading
way too much into this.
She's probably fine!
Besides, there's no reason
for me to go and see her now.
She'd think something
weird was going on.
If it's an excuse
you're looking for,
I can give you one.
[JINTO sighs]
You mean Diaho? Thanks a lot.
[meows]
It must be nice
to be so carefree.
[meows]
Huh? Is there
somebody out there?
[JINTO]
Lafiel? Are you okay?
Is Diaho bothering you?
[LAFIEL sighs]
Hey...
[LAFIEL] I don't know why you're
all so worried about me.
Worried about you?
What are you talkin' about?
[LAFIEL] Hm. Nothing.
It's fine. Just forget it.
[yawns]
Glad to see I have such an
effect when I come into a room!
Falling asleep!
[LAFIEL]
Jinto?
[JINTO]
Yeah, what?
[LAFIEL]
What's for dinner tonight?
[JINTO]
Huh? That's easy!
Why don't you just look
at your online menu?
It's all there.
[LAFIEL]
Yeah?
It's hard to concentrate
with you standing
over my shoulder.
Sorry. Let me check.
It looks like the main
course is some sort of
spicy lamb dish.
Do you wanna know
what else it comes with?
[LAFIEL]
No thank you.
Jinto, if you've got
something to say,
why don't you just say it?
[JINTO] Because I don't
know what to say.
Can I sit down here?
Suit yourself--
sit where you like.
That's great, thanks.
It's about the battle
simulation we just did...
[LAFIEL] You can't tell me
anything I don't already know.
I know that losing
to someone as good as
Hecto-Commander Kotokeil
isn't a surprise.
I don't need to
hear it from you.
I wasn't going to.
But if you're gonna
be down in the dumps,
you shouldn't do it
in front of the crew.
"Down in the dumps"?
What do you mean?
[JINTO] They're concerned
that if you, as the captian,
are depressed after
this little setback,
then it's not a good
sign for the future.
Do you think that, too?
No, not me.
You may remember I've seen
a certain imperial princess
feeling a little like
this before--if not worse.
Three years ago...
Okay, I've heard enough of this.
[JINTO] What? I thought you
didn't like me sitting here
not saying anything.
I said I've heard enough.
Not that you ever really
listen to me anyway.
You're right about that.
Look, I've gotta say this,
so please just listen
to me for a minute.
I can understand why
the crew are concerned.
If you get this downhearted
when you lose in a simulation
against someone you had
no chance of beating anyway,
how are you gonna react
if you lose a real battle?
[LAFIEL] If that ever happens,
I'll just back off.
I know what to do.
[JINTO]
Sure you know what to do--
it's just that not everyone's
convinced about that.
Everyone... Everyone...
Are you part of this "everyone"?
Are you worried about me, too?
Not at all.
I think you're mature
enough to know
when it's okay to feel
dejected and when it's not.
Or at least, you were three
years ago, and I can't believe
you've changed that
much since then.
Yeah, I'm going to be fine.
You know, you seem
to have become
rather full of yourself
since I last saw you.
I like to think of it as being
grown up and responsible.
But if you wanna call it
being too full of yourself...
...then I might as well
live up to the name
and tell you I think you're
simply not used to losing.
You're so used to
getting your own way
that when you lost
in that simulation today,
you couldn't just deal with it.
You're acting like
a spoiled kid.
Next time it happens,
don't be such a sore loser
and everyone will feel
differently. Understand?
Idiot!
[JINTO] Anyway, I guess
I should be going now.
Listen, Jinto.
I wish you'd stop acting like
you're my father or something.
Is it that bad?
Yes. I don't need
looking after anymore.
[JINTO]
You've got it all backwards.
Look, we're up in space, right?
This is your home territory.
The home of your
people, the Abh.
I'm just a mere Lander,
so up here in space,
I believe what you say
and follow wherever you go.
You could at least sound
a little bit sincere.
Then I might actually believe
you meant what you said.
I did mean it--why won't
you just trust me, Lafiel?
Why won't you believe me?
It's the truth.
Anyway, see you later.
[LAFIEL]
Jinto.
[JINTO]
Yes?
Nothing... No, it's nothing.
Okay.
[LAFIEL]
Three years ago,
we looked out for
each other all the time.
How can things
change so quickly?
[JINTO]
Three years ago...
That was when I first saw her.
My patrol ship, Gosroth ,
is awaiting you.
Please come with me immediately.
[JINTO]
Afterwards, we walked together.
We laughed together.
We cried together.
[LAFIEL]
Jinto!
You pig! I'll get you for this!
No, Lafiel! Stay back!
[KAIT]
They're over there!
Don't let them get away!
[PILOT 1A] We can't get any
closer! It's too dangerous!
I don't care! Ram them!
Just fly straight into them!
Ah!
Damn you!
[KAIT]
Damn you all!
[JINTO] But eventually,
our adventures together
had to come to an end.
And by then,
I had lost my family, my home,
and any connection
I had with my past.
[RAMAJ] The Battle of
Sufugnoff was just a decoy,
drawing our attention away from
a larger attack on the Capital.
We managed to drive them
away but not before
incurring major losses.
[FARAMUNSH] The regions
surrounding the empire
have now been annexed
by enemy forces
and they've also severed all
our transportation links.
[RAMAJ] So they've
completely cut us off.
[FARAMUNSH]
I'm afraid so.
And we don't have
enough military power
left to do anything about it.
We're completely
at their mercy now.
[JINTO] It was strange how
this news affected me--
I wasn't upset or angry about
being cut off from my home.
If anything, I felt a sense
of relief. How weird is that?
They say that good can
come from every situation,
and well, I did meet you again!
You shall call me Lafiel!
Captain!
We'll be passing through
the Vobeirunei Gate
at any moment now!
[SOBAASH]
Ten seconds.
Eight...
...7...
I want you to give me
a visual on screen!
[SOBAASH]
...4, 3, 2, 1.
We've passed through!
[LAFIEL] This is Battleship
number 18 Basroil
under the Exercise
and Training Fleet.
We have passed through
the Vobeirunei Gate.
[KOTOKEIL]
Very good.
Now join the Battleship
Squadron stationed at 5001.
Wait there until all
ships have assembled.
[LAFIEL]
Roger.
We will proceed to 5001 and
await further instructions.
[FAAKON] Deca-Commander!
You've gotta see this!
Oh, wow!
Surely they can't all be waiting
to get into formation?
So this is it.
The Naval Station of Vobeirunei.
Over the past three
years, the empire
has been rebuilding its fleet.
At times, the pace of the
reconstruction was so rapid,
that it was almost
like fireflies hatching
during breeding season.
Ship after ship.
The fleet soon reached
a level of grandeur
that had never been seen before.
It was several times larger
than even before the war began.
Every single day,
the fleet is reorganized
and every single week,
a new squadron is formed.
Of course, some of the
ships will head out to war
never to return.
The day will soon arrive
for our ship to leave.
And our battle will begin.
[JINTO] It feels so good to be
with you once again, Lafiel.
I always wanna be there for you,
through thick and thin,
through good times
and bad times.
I know I'll grow old
more quickly than you,
because I'm only a Lander.
But to me, that doesn't matter.
I'll be there. If you become
Empress, I'll be there.
If we get turned into dust
in the emptiness of space,
I'll be there.
Whether you like it or not!
[JINTO] What we do with the
freedom we have been given
ultimately determines
the value of our lives,
and I have chosen to use my
freedom to follow you, Lafiel.
[JINTO] A friend of mine,
Ku Dorin, once told me
that I'd given up my freedom
far too early in my life,
but I don't feel like
I've given up my freedom--
I feel like I'm gaining it!
I don't believe I will ever
have such a wonderful
opportunity again!
[JINTO] I wish you could
understand this better, Lafiel.
You've never experienced
true freedom.
The price you pay for being born
into the Imperial Royal family.
You have to seize the day,
or that day may pass you by.
We have been assigned
to the first squadron
of Battleship Battalion
Latouche 1058.
We will leave in 12 hours.
Commence preparations
for departure.
[sighs] I've never heard
anything so boring.
There's nothing worse than
a dull, but well-meaning
president attempting to speak
passionately about his planet.
[ALL panting]
You do know that she's
the younger sister
of Baron Febdash.
Huh?
How far will we get
before the enemy strikes?
How far...?