[NARRATOR speaking Baronh]
[LAFIEL]
When I was still a child,
we always played the same game
in the zero-gravity garden.
[CHILDREN chattering, laughing]
[whistle blows]
[LAFIEL]
To win the game
you had to knock your
opponent's lance away.
It sounds easy, but it was rare
for a game to finish quickly.
The players would repeatedly
launch themselves
at each other, only making
contact with their lances.
Eventually, one of them
would lose their balance,
or simply be overpowered,
and the lance
would get knocked
out of their hands.
[LAFIEL]
This game was known as jousting.
[SHIDORYUA]
You're leaving?
[GUEN] Yes, my term of office
is due to end shortly.
Therefore, I would like you,
as Prime Minister,
to convey a message
of farewell to
her Imperial Highness
the Empress.
[SHIDORYUA] I'm sure that won't
be a problem, Ambassador.
During the past three years, the
only country to have retained
diplomatic ties with
the Empire was yours--
the Federation of Hania.
[GUEN] Prime Minister,
I want you to understand
that our country did not ally
ourselves to those countries
whom we consider
respectable simply
so we could take
part in the war.
However, the fact remains
that we are still members
of the Nova Sicily
Treaty Organization.
Of course. I'm well aware
of that fact, Ambassador.
But you have to admit
that your country
does act quite differently
from the other countries
within the Treaty,
so you must forgive me if your
alliance with them happens
to slip my mind occasionally.
Oh...?
And what exactly do you
mean by acting differently?
[SHIDORYUA] Other countries
within the treaty
have a tendency to
trivialize any differences
in our political systems.
For instance,
the difference between
imperialism and democracy.
But that is a vast difference
which produces a huge gulf
between those other
countries and our Empire.
I don't suppose that has
anything to do with why you,
a Lander, wanted to achieve
the highest rank possible
in the Empire's
political system?
[SHIDORYUA] Hm. I suppose
you could put it that way.
But, instead...
...what do you think
of this for a reason?
The Empire is the only
force around that is able
to curtail the onslaught
of the modern era,
which is advancing
on our worlds
with the power of
a raging dragon.
Do you follow me?
Hm. I'm not sure I understand
what you're suggesting,
Prime Minister.
[SHIDORYUA]
Really?
But then I suppose it's wise
for you to be cautious.
[CREW 11A]
Assault Units! Pull back!
[JINTO] Our ship, the Basroil,
was still in the middle
of a battle to defend
the Aptic Gate.
[sighs]
With the guard ships
on the front line,
things have become
a lot easier for us.
Yes. Did the ship
suffer any damage?
The armor plating was hit in
23 places, and there were
slight pressure leaks in
seven of those, Captain.
But they've already
been taken care of.
What about propulsion,
engine, and weaponry?
[SAMSON]
No problems to report.
[JINTO] All personnel are
alive and accounted for.
Well, that's a relief!
There's a message.
All ships in the
First Assault Unit!
We are to make a
temporary retreat.
Approval has been
given from Battle HQ.
[LAFIEL]
No way!
[JINTO]
Huh?
Commander! We are ready,
able, and willing to fight!
[ATOSURYUA]
Deca-Commander Abriel...
I'm afraid you
don't understand.
We can make a
temporary retreat
precisely because we're still
in a position to fight.
If you haven't seen enough
of the battlefield yet,
don't worry--they'll be plenty
more opportunities ahead.
I understand.
[ATOSURYUA] Good. If there
are no more queries,
we'll begin to retreat at
maximum battle speed.
The route will be
transmitted to you.
Excuse me.
Captain?
Yes, of course.
Retreat.
[LAFIEL grunts]
[LAFIEL gasps]
[LAFIEL]
The shame of it!
Uh!
[JINTO]
Tastes good?!
[LAFIEL]
Huh?
I thought that maybe
a nice cold drink
would be good for you right now.
And so I took the liberty
of getting you one.
But if you want to drink
your own blood, go ahead!
I don't know what
you're talking about.
What are you insinuating?
[JINTO]
Oh, nothing!
It's just that it looked like
you were getting thirsty
for something more
than a cold drink.
But I'd draw the line at blood!
Of course. I would, too!
Oh, so you mean you weren't
hungry for blood after all!
No! Of course not!
All right, no need
to bite my head off!
It was only a joke!
[SAMSON]
Captain!
Sorry to interrupt this
entertaining conversation,
but could you give
the crew permission
to remove their pressure suits?
The danger has passed
for the moment
and working in
those suits can be
fairly uncomfortable for them.
[LAFIEL]
Sorry, I didn't think of that.
Permission granted.
Why, thank you, great lady!
And why was our
conversation so entertaining?
No reason.
Just sounded like you two
were havin' fun back there.
[NEFEE] It appears we
severely underestimated
the number of mines the enemy
had available to them.
So, the mine attacks
are continuing?
It's a completely
irrational way to fight.
I'd prefer to win irrationally
than to lose a simply because
we were being rational.
[NEREIS]
That goes for me, too.
But in this instance, we
don't have any say over how
the enemy chooses to fight.
Our patrol ships
will undoubtedly
run out of mines soon.
[NEREIS] Give them permission to
use the electromagnetic cannons.
[NEFEE] Yes, I suppose that's
the most rational response.
I'll let them know right
away and give the order
before you have time
to change your mind
and think up something
completely irrational.
[NEREIS] Three hours until
the main fleet arrives...
[NEREIS] I hope we can we
hold them off until then.
[KENESH] Our forces still have
control of the Aptic region.
[KENESH] The Fourth Fleet is
approaching from the right wing
to cover the path between
Wimpel and Aptic.
Once the enemy has gone through,
Admiral Kotoponi will then
close in behind and
cut off that route.
The Second Fleet, which is
commanded by Admiral Rulef,
is currently heading to the
battlefield from the left wing.
They are making their
way from the Mystel Gate
to the Aptic Gate.
[DUSANYU]
Mystel will be safe now.
I think we should let
Admiral Mulusafa know
that he can come out of hiding.
As soon as he
receives his orders,
the Mystel Defense
Fleet will become
the Seventeenth Fleet of
Operation Phantom Flame.
Yes, sir.
[sighs] Looks like we'll
arrive just in time.
That reminds me.
We've got Viscountess Paryunu
stationed in the Aptic region.
And the young Count Hyde...
If I remember correctly,
he's also on board her ship.
[DUSANYU sighs] I hope
those two are still alive.
If either of them were
to die under my command,
I don't think I would be
able to sleep at night.
[KRAN] Hey, I'm not getting
any increase in output!
[PAVERYUA]
Okay... A little to the right.
No, left! Left!
[KRAN]
Keep your hair on!
You sound like my mother!
Hey, be careful!
You gotta take it
easy on that thing!
[SAMSON] This engine
room's a delicate creature.
You've gotta treat it like
you were stroking a cat.
[CREW]
Okay...
Anyway, please load as
much stuff as you can.
We don't know when we're
gonna be refueling again.
[CAT meows]
[LAFIEL]
Diaho? Is that you?
I'll get you out of there.
Just stay there--
it won't take a moment.
You shouldn't wander
around like that.
You might get lost. And if the
crew's forced to abandon ship,
we don't want to
leave you behind
because we can't find you.
Although... I hope we're
never in a position
to need to do anything drastic
like having to abandon ship.
[BEIKAL growls]
[gasps]
In the same way that
you, as a Princess,
have responsibilities
and duties to your subjects,
I, as an Officer of
the Star Forces,
am responsible for my crew.
It's the Princess...
She just saved our hide!
I guess we're even.
So, what do you think?
Have I really got what it takes
to be Captain of the ship?
[meows]
You think so?!
But, no. As much as I'd like to,
I don't think I can
really trust your opinion.
This situation is getting
more serious by the minute.
[NEFEE] It looks like the
patrol ships are running
out of ammunition for their
electro-magnetic cannons.
[NEREIS]
Running out of ammunition?
But we were planning
to save those cannons
until the enemy ships actually
arrived on the scene.
I can't believe we
allowed this to happen.
So, what are we going to do?
Don't you have any ideas?
[NEFEE] We'll have to
conserve ammunition.
You don't seriously expect me
to order the fleet to do that?
How humiliating!
It's less humiliating
than losing ships
because we ran out of ammo.
Wouldn't you agree, Brother?
I know what we'll do.
Issue an order forbidding
all ships from using
their electro-magnetic
cannons against the mines.
[NEFEE] But that will only
increase the burden
placed on the guard ships.
[NEREIS] There's nothing
we can do about that.
Once the enemy arrives,
the guard ships
can take a back seat and
let the others take their turn.
I suppose you're right...
We've located a large number
of enemy ships coming
from the Sord, sir!
And so the moment of
truth has arrived.
The battle is about to
enter a new phase.
[NEREIS grunts] Guard ships
to retreat immediately!
Look at that! They've run
out of ammunition, too.
[NEREIS]
That's not what I said.
Even if the guard ships have
used up all their mines,
they still have plenty
of nuclear-fusion bombs
available to them.
[NEFEE]
I know that, Nereis.
But don't you think that
sometimes it would be nice
to relax knowing you
had the upper hand?
This is the moment you've
all been waiting for!
The time to fight against
enemy ships has arrived!
[ATOSURYUA] Up to now, your
battles have been against
mines and patrol ships--
hardly difficult opponents.
But this time, the
enemy's assault vessels
will be your foe!
[ATOSURYUA]
If any of you don't keep up,
I intend to take it personally!
[LAFIEL]
I wonder if I'll ever be able
to feel completely calm
during a battle.
[LAFIEL growls]
Hey, I just realized--
we won't have to worry
about being attacked by
dormant mines anymore!
You're right. With the
information provided
by the Command, we're in a
position to identify them now.
We can safely let the Second
Aviator deal with them.
[LAFIEL gasps]
[MOONIJU]
This is Captain Mooniju
of the 2107th Guard Fleet.
We're under attack from
enemy assault vessels.
Request backup immediately!
[growls]
[ATOSURYUA] All ships proceed
at maximum battle speed!
Cut off the enemy fleet's
access to the guard ships!
Main engine, full power!
[ATOSURYUA]
There are six enemy ships.
That puts us at a disadvantage,
but it can't be helped.
We will identify the enemy
ships from right to left
as Enemy One to Six.
We will attack Enemy Six first,
and then turn back
and immediately
attack Enemy One!
Yes, Commander!
[SOBAASH] The enemy has moved
into a cluster formation
with Enemy Six in the middle.
Fire!
[CREW grunting]
Enemy Six has been destroyed.
Hold on!
We're about to fly through
the gas in the debris!
Something's wrong on the
outside of the ship!
The temperature's rising
to dangerous levels!
Any hotter and the
armor will melt!
Well, do something about it!
After we've passed
through this...
[SAMSON]
Yeah, but what?
Increase capacity of all
cooling mechanisms...
[SOBAASH] Passing through
the gases in 5 seconds...
4...3...
...2...
...1...
We've passed through!
[LAFIEL]
Turn around! [grunts]
Lafiel! It's too far for us!
[ATOSURYUA]
Would you look at that...
The enemy ships have
turned around, too.
That means they want
to continue fighting.
Okay, everyone, hang in there!
[ATOSURYUA] Our next target
is still Enemy One!
Main engine! Accelerate!
[LAFIEL]
I always wondered why jousting
was such a fun game to play
when I was a child.
Now, I think I understand
where it comes from...
[EKURYUA]
The enemy is approaching again
in a cluster formation.
[ATOSURYUA]
Calling all ships.
Our next goal is to
reduce their numbers
so that we're on
an even footing.
If we can't do that, then we'll
have to retreat, understand?
And then we...
Well, if we can hang in there,
we can set our sights
on Enemy Three.
[LAFIEL]
Mm-hm. Hm?
The Unit Commander's obviously
being quite cautious about this.
I have to say, I'm relieved!
She's right to be cautious.
Because we struck first,
we went from four against six
to four against five.
But that's our limit if we're
going to fight head-on.
If we lost just one ship,
we wouldn't stand a chance.
Yeah, that sounds about right.
There's an enemy
fleet approaching!
The enemy ships appear
to be targeting
their attack on the Gamroil !
Fire!
Use the laser cannons!
Gamroil ! Are you okay?!
[ATOSURYUA]
We're fine.
There's a change in plan!
Aim your attack on Enemy One.
We're finishing them off!
All ships turn around!
[CREW groaning]
[SAMSON] Captain! The engines
can't take much more of this!
They have to keep going
until the battle's over!
Okay.
Captain! Enemy One's retreating
in the direction of
the Aptic Gate!
[ATOSURYUA] Looks like we caused
more extensive damage
than we originally thought!
Now it's four against four.
Another change in plan!
We'll focus on attacking
Enemy Three!
It is my firm belief that when
we have equal numbers
it is impossible for the
Star Forces to lose a battle!
Certainly not my squadron.
And not any ship I'm Captain of!
[CREW groans]
All ships turn around!
[LAFIEL panting]
[ATOSURYUA]
It looks like we're starting
to run out of fuel
and ammunition.
If we can't destroy Enemy
Three in the next attack,
then we have to
retreat, understood?
Don't waste any time
in pulling out.
I'm not gonna run away.
[JINTO]
Lafiel...
[EKURYUA]
Enemy ships approaching!
I've never lost...
I've never lost a battle!
Now! [grunts]
[LAFIEL gasps]
[LAFIEL]
They're firing at us!
Okay crew, brace yourselves!
This is gonna be tough!
[LAFIEL gasps]
[NEREIS] Do you want us
to just sit here and wait
while the enemy goes ahead
and destroys us, Nefee?
Where do you think you're going?
It would be a great dishonor
to discover that I'd let
my men die in vain.
But at least I would
like to choose
where I end my days.
[LAFIEL]
Permission is granted to take
any steps necessary.
All hands! Abandon ship!