Prepare to fire the
anti-proton cannon!
Preparations for opening
the front port complete!
[SOBAASH]
Opening now!
[SOBAASH] Safety devices
for number five and six
have been released!
[LAFIEL]
Get the laser cannons ready!
[SOBAASH]
We have less than 20 seconds
before space-time fusion.
[SOBAASH]
Ten...
Nine...
Eight...
Seven...
Six...
Five...
Four...
Three...
Two...
One.
Space-time fusion!
All ships, attack!
[NARRATOR speaking Baronh]
The first group of
mines has been
confirmed as destroyed.
[sighs]
Our first orders
have been carried out.
Initiate space-time separation!
Starting space-time separation!
[SAMSON]
That wasn't so bad!
Finally, we're
seeing some action.
Unfortunately, while we
were watching out
for mines, the enemy ship
has moved further ahead.
Captain, there's been
a message from command.
They want us in single
column formation.
Senior Aviator!
Single column formation!
Roger, Captain.
[LAFIEL] Our assault ship
squadrons are hunting down
the enemy patrol
ships one by one.
[JINTO] This situation
reminds me of something.
It's just like the time
we were on the Gosroth .
[LAFIEL]
Hm.
[LAFIEL] Just because
we survived that time
doesn't mean we'll be safe here.
This time we're at the
forefront of the battle.
If we manage to get out of
this without any casualties...
...it'll be a miracle.
It wouldn't surprise me...
if they wiped us out.
You know, you haven't
changed one bit.
[LAFIEL]
Hm?
To be totally honest with you,
I'm finding this whole
situation pretty scary.
And if I'm honest with you...
...it scares me, too.
Knowing I'm not the only
one makes me feel better.
Huh?
How could knowing
that I'm afraid
possibly make you
feel any better?
Well... that's a good question!
I suppose it's nice knowing
you're not on your own--
it makes things
easier to handle.
It would seem kind of unfair
if I was the only one
who was afraid!
Well, maybe...
But I don't think
there's anyone here
who isn't afraid.
Perhaps with the exception
of your cat over there.
The only time Diaho's
afraid is when it's time
for him to have his bath--
he's petrified by the idea!
[JINTO] Yeah, it's true...
We are all afraid.
Except maybe one
person on this ship,
who has some
experience in battle.
Samson, who survived the battle
at Scaresche Gate
three years ago.
We have 12 minutes
until we experience
space-time fusion
with the enemy!
[LAFIEL]
Hm.
[LAFIEL] I can't believe we're
seriously going to attack
all those enemy patrol
ships when we only have
six ships in our squadron!
Some people would
call it brave--
others would call it suicidal.
The lead ship Gamroil has begun
to decrease its speed.
[sighs] What a relief!
I thought our six assault ships
were gonna have to
fight the enemy alone!
I expect we're holding back
so the other squadrons
can catch up with us.
It's a good thing
Hecto-Commander Asuryua
knows what she's doing here.
There's been a change
to the schedule
for space-time fusion.
[SOBAASH] The 4th assault
unit is approaching!
[EKURYUA] Transmission received
requesting us to move
into a parallel formation.
[LAFIEL] Senior Aviator,
I'll leave that to you.
[SOBAASH]
Roger!
Estimated time until
space-time fusion is now...
...ten minutes.
I guess we just
have to sit tight
for the next ten minutes.
Yes.
[EKURYUA] The 2nd and 5th
assault units have entered
into space-time fusion with
the enemy patrol ships.
[LAFIEL] It's like a pack
of animals waiting
to launch an attack
on their prey.
You ever see
somethin' like that?
Not in real life--
just in a documentary.
[JINTO]
Hm.
Looks to me like it's all over.
Yes.
We did suffer casualties,
but our side was victorious.
Everyone, it's our turn next!
Captain! The enemy ship's
space-time bubble has divided!
There's now four of them!
They're probably mines!
I'm surprised they
had some left.
Releasing those
mines was probably
an act of desperation,
only done as a last resort.
And what does
Squadron Command say?
We've heard nothing yet.
Wait, here's something now.
It's a message coming
from headquarters.
It says, "Do what
you have to do."
I see.
[LAFIEL]
This is like last time.
We can't enter space-time fusion
and just wait for
them to attack us.
Jinto, you shall quickly
return to your position.
You'll be in charge of
monitoring the air pressure
on the ship and treating
any casualties.
But those mines are headed
straight for us, aren't they?!
If we get hit by one of them,
we're gonna be blown to pieces!
I don't think there's
anything I can do to help
if that happens.
I suppose that's true.
Well, do what you want.
Just make sure you're
steady on your feet
and keep out the way.
If you fall over,
land on top of me
and distract me somehow,
you'll be the death of us all!
I'll be careful.
The space-time bubbles suspected
as enemy mines approaching!
They've passed by
the side of the Gamroil ,
and are heading this way!
Distance: five...
...4...
...3.5...
...3.2...
...3.1...
...3.3...
The enemy space-time bubbles
have gone right past us!
[BOTH sighs]
That was close!
At least we avoided
the shame of dying
in our first battle ever!
The enemy space-time bubbles!
They're entering
space-time fusion
with the ship at the rear!
[gasps] Is it the Leekroil ?
No, it's the Kidroil .
[KIDROIL PILOT] Confirmation
of space-time fusion
with third enemy ship!
Our ship appears to be
a very attractive target
for those enemy mines.
Prepare to counterattack
with the laser cannons
as soon as you're all ready!
Aim the bow of the ship
at the first mine!
Fire the anti-proton cannon
at the first mine.
As soon as that's destroyed,
fire at the third!
[CREW groaning]
It's not over yet!
They're still fighting!
The last mine entered
space-time fusion.
[ATOSURYUA] Calling the
Kidroil ! Captain Beikal!
Do you have time to answer me?
I think that's about all I've
got time for, Commander,
and that's being
extremely optimistic.
I don't want to hear
you talking like that!
You'll survive this!
That last mine is heading
straight towards us
on the port side!
Fire the laser cannon now!
[gasps]
The sixth ship of
the 4th assault unit
has vanished from the screen!
What about the Kidroil ?
[SOBAASH]
Checking now.
The fighting has stopped...
and the Kidroil ...
They're still alive!
I see.
[SOBAASH]
However...
They're moving very slowly now.
[BEIKAL] Damn! The remnants
of those mines are too heavy.
[ATOSURYUA] Kidroil !
It appears that the weight
of your space-time
bubble has increased!
I apologize, Commander.
But moving at this rate,
we're not going to be able
to keep up with you and
the rest of the squadron.
I understand.
But I'm expecting great things
from you in the next battle!
[BEIKAL sighs]
[SOBAASH] The Kidroil
is getting further behind!
[LAFIEL] Looks like the
commander has no intention
of slowing down.
Seven minutes until we enter
space-time fusion
with the enemy ship!
That makes it ten of us
against one of them.
The odds should be in our favor.
[LAFIEL] This is getting
to be more and more like
the situation on the Gosroth .
[JINTO] So, we have to win
this one, don't we?
Where's your common sense?
You should think
before you speak!
Of course we have to win--
when is it ever okay to lose?
I guess you're right about that!
Six minutes until
space-time fusion!
Jinto, the best thing
for you is to return
to your station. Once we're in
action against an enemy ship,
there'll be things
for you to do.
Okay. Right away!
[LAFIEL]
Hm.
[LAFIEL] That's strange!
I'm not frightened anymore!
[LAFIEL]
Was that why he came on board?
[LAFIEL] No--that would be
far too thoughtful for him!
All of us here on the
Basroil will commence
the first phase of battle
as soon as we enter
into space-time fusion
with the enemy patrol ship.
This will be in five minutes.
Battle stations, everyone!
[SOBAASH] One minute until
space-time fusion!
The lead ship, the Gamroil ,
will achieve space-time
fusion in 32 seconds.
I want you to establish
a communication link
with the Gamroil as soon as
we enter space-time fusion.
Yes, Captain!
[SOBAASH] The Gamroil has
entered space-time fusion!
We'll be there in 15 seconds!
Countdown--ten seconds!
Nine...
Eight...
Seven...
Six...
Five...
Four...
Three...
Two...
One.
Space-time fusion!
[LAFIEL gasps]
Damn, they've already
destroyed one of ours!
[EKURYUA] Receiving transmission
from the Gamroil !
Time to put your
training into practice,
Deca-Commander Abriel.
Proceed to your
position as planned!
Yes, Commander!
[JINTO] They've fired their
laser cannon at us!
Whoa! That was a little
too close for comfort!
[sighs]
[EKURYUA]
Our defensive magnetic shield
is designed to
repel laser cannons,
so I don't know what
you're worried about.
Yeah, but the ship can still
sustain damage, can't it?
[SOBAASH]
Enemy ship ahead!
[gasps]
We scored a direct hit,
but there seems
to be minimal damage.
[LAFIEL growls]
Now arriving in
position as planned!
Okay, everybody,
let's get at 'em!
Shoot like crazy!
I've got a job for you!
Jinto, you can monitor
the engines during battle!
[LAFIEL grunts]
[BEIKAL]
Damn!
Even the princess
is getting a chance
to show how she can fight!
[growls]
[BEIKAL]
We're not even in the arena!
One of our ships has been
destroyed by the enemy!
Which one went down?
The second ship
of the fourth squadron.
Whether the crew escaped...
...remains unconfirmed.
[JINTO] Now there's only
eight of us left.
Watch out! The enemy's
laser cannons...
They're focussed
in our direction!
Increase output of the
defensive magnetic shield!
[ALL grunting]
Is there any damage?
Storage area 14 was hit,
but I think we're okay!
No one was in there,
and the pressure has
been maintained.
What do you mean we're okay?
We keep a lot of valuable
spare parts for our equipment
in that storage area!
Keep your fingers crossed
they haven't been destroyed.
But I'm sure we can replace
anything that's broken!
[SAMSON] Some of those
parts are brand new!
Don't you understand
how painful it is
for an engineer like me, seeing
all that stuff go to waste?
Huh?
[LAFIEL]
Hm...
So that's the way
our experienced pilot
handles his fear.
[SOBAASH] Four electro-magnetic
cannon shots
headed for the Helzroil !
They're going to be hit!
[ATOSURYUA]
Helzroil , you have permission
to temporarily leave
the battlefield!
Hurry up and get
out of the bubble!
[GAMROIL 2nd OFFICER]
We've just had confirmation
that the Helzroil
has been destroyed.
They must've retreated too late!
I can't have casualties
in my squadron!
[GAMROIL 2nd OFFICER]
The enemy ship has suddenly
changed direction!
It looks like their target's
going to be... the Basroil !
[SOBAASH]
We're being targeted
by their electro-
magnetic cannon!
[ATOSURYUA] Basroil , you have
permission to temporarily
leave the battlefield!
[JINTO]
Lafiel!
Space-time separation!
Hurry it up!
They've fired the cannon!
Doesn't look good.
[LAFIEL]
Engines, full power!
Fire anti-proton cannon!
[CREW grunts]
No!
Space-time separation
in ten seconds!
Nine...
Eight...
Seven...
Six...
Five...
Four...
Three...
Two...
One...
Separation!
We made it out alive.
Only just--it was close.
[LAFIEL]
Yes it was.
I can see the other
assault ships.
They're merging their
space-time bubbles
with the enemy patrol ship now.
[sighs] I guess they don't
need our services anymore.
[LAFIEL gasps]
We have to re-enter
the space-time bubble!
The commander only
gave us permission
to leave the
battlefield temporarily!
We have to get back in there!
Right away, Captain!
I don't believe it!
Couldn't we have just
let the other ships
deal with the rest
of the battle?
Space-time fusion!
[JINTO] They don't even
have enough power left
to keep their magnetic
shield working.
It's a massacre.
It doesn't seem fair at all.
I don't like to fight this way.
[EKURYUA] It doesn't matter
whether you like it or not.
Assault ships like these
aren't very strong.
This is the best way to
fight against patrol ships
which are more powerful
than we are.
I'm sorry, Captain.
You're right. Of course it is.
I hope there's time
for one more shot.
[ATOSURYUA] Basroil !
All ships are to retreat!
I'm sorry--I know you've only
just re-entered the battlefield.
All ships!
Separate from the space-time
bubble immediately!
Why are we giving up now
when we're so close
to destroying them?!
You're right, I know.
However, we received
these orders
directly from headquarters.
The battleship squadron
is ready for action
on the front line.
They've decided to use mines
to destroy the patrol
ship we were after.
[LAFIEL]
Very well. I understand.
Prepare for
space-time separation.
Roger.
You okay, Captain?
They've made the right decision.
The fact that we nearly
destroyed that patrol ship
isn't important--after all,
if we'd carried on,
we'd have run the risk of losing
another one or two of our ships.
Using mines means there
will be no more casualties.
It's definitely the most
sensible course of action.
[SOBAASH]
Space-time separation!
[EKURYUA]
Mine attacks have now commenced.
[SAMSON]
What a sight!
Enemy patrol ship is destroyed.
[LAFIEL] Perhaps our role
as an assault ship squadron
is not to fight, but simply
to keep the enemy at bay.
[JINTO]
Captain...
[LAFIEL]
Huh?
I think we should all
get ourselves a drink.
And then we should have a toast!
What do you mean "a toast"?
What is there to celebrate?
We didn't win a battle.
Yes, I know we didn't.
But we should celebrate
surviving our first campaign!
[LAFIEL]
Hm. Well... maybe you're right.
Sounds good to me.
A drink?!
That's very thoughtful
of you, my boy!
You're welcome! But nothing
alcoholic, right, Captain?
[CREW laughs]
[JINTO]
So...
Here on the assault
ship Basroil ,
we had successfully survived
our first campaign!
[JINTO] And I believe that
survival is an achievement
worth celebrating!
[JINTO] But while we were
fighting in one section
of the battlefield,
the relative period of calm
elsewhere was coming to an end.
The machinery of war
was moving into action.
The United Mankind managed
to send out
reconnaissance missions
to five different
planet systems,
including the Aptic system.
That's a lot of manpower,
but we didn't destroy them all.
[KENESH] We were successful
in eliminating
about half of them.
The remaining ships
probably returned
to the United Mankind with
important information.
[DUSANYU]
That cannot be helped.
However, these reconnaissance
missions of theirs
can be useful to us.
Surely we discovered
valuable information
about the strength of
their fleets from this?
Absolutely correct.
According to the analysis
made by the chief
of our Communications
Department,
the enemy's numbers
fall somewhere between
180 and 200 squadrons.
[DUSANYU gasps]
[DUSANYU]
Maybe I've underestimated them.
[DUSANYU] Allow me to consider
this for a moment.
I'll return to the
bridge shortly.
Very good, sir. Understood.
[DUSANYU] The enemy appears
to be recovering quickly.
This would suggest they
had some inside knowledge
of our plans.
But if they didn't,
then the situation is
much more worrying,
because that would mean
that the massive fleet
in this area is just
the tip of the iceberg.
In that case, there's only
one course of action open to us.
[JINTO] The battle that
the Basroil was involved in
was only one small part
of the operation.
As soon as we had finished
our first campaign
and were getting ready
for a well-deserved rest,
Operation Phantom Flame
moved into the next phase.
[NEREIS]
Are they worthy of us?
[NEFEE]
I think so.
Lafiel! I...!
I've heard people say
his chief of staff
is also a Bebaus.
So we're outta luck!
You think there's
some common sense
in that head of yours,
right, Nereis?
Huh?
Are you saying I
haven't got any? Nefee?
[JINTO yelps]
[DUSANYU]
Why don't we let Admiral Bebaus
head up that creak?
A person with many loves
will not be promoted.