[NARRATOR speaking Baronh]
[SAMSON]
Mines?!
In a place like this?!
Second Aviator!
Firing!
[CREW grunting]
[LAFIEL gasps]
Enemy attack?!
Is it a direct hit?!
[SOBAASH] Second enemy ship:
space-time fusion!
Third enemy ship:
[SOBAASH] Fourth and fifth
enemy ships approaching!
Fire the anti-proton
cannon and then aim it
at the fourth ship!
Roger!
[LAFIEL]
Fire!
The ship will respond
in five seconds!
The fourth enemy ship has
achieved space-time fusion!
[SOBAASH] The fifth
enemy ship has achieved
space-time fusion!
Fire the rear laser cannons!
The enemy assault ship's
focusing its attack on us!
We need more shield
on the right hull.
Shoot them down with
the anti-proton cannon!
The ship will respond
in ten seconds!
Eight...
Seven...
Six...
--Five... Four...
--We're not gonna make it!
Three...
[gasps]
There's a message
from the Seigroil .
[RAGASH] I hope we didn't
intrude by helping you
out there, Basroil !
Not at all.
Thank you, Captain Ragash.
No problem.
You know, you weren't doing
too badly for a newcomer.
Uh-- Oh...
Watch out behind you!
Direction 172 degrees,
24 minutes.
Shoot it down immediately
with the laser cannon!
[KENESH] To be honest
with you, the First Fleet,
led by Admiral Spoor,
had almost achieved
its objectives in
Operation Phantom Flame.
However, it appears
the enemy has been
undertaking further
reconnaissance missions.
We're certain they're preparing
a large-scale counterattack.
If the First Fleet
cannot make it as far
as the Laseese Kingdom,
the gates behind them
are liable to be
retaken by the enemy,
cutting off our supply line
and leaving the fleet stranded.
The logical choice
would be for us to halt
the advances of the First Fleet
and wait for the enemy
to make their first move.
In the current
situation, the places
most likely to be
targeted for attack
are the gates nearest
to the enemy:
Wimpel Gate and Miofrantia Gate.
If we retreat from these gates,
leaving only some
reconnaissance ships in place,
then the only place
they can attack us
is at the connecting gates
of Aptic and Mystel,
where we have time to
build a strong defense.
If we can defend these
gates, we can safely
secure our supply line.
Of course, it will take
time for the enemy
to rebuild their fleet.
During that time,
we can easily carry out
our operation.
[OFFICER 7A] Assuming
we're able to successfully
win the battle that lies
ahead of us, that is.
That's why the chief
of staff is here today--
to outline our battle plans.
[OFFICER 7A]
No, that's not what I meant.
Chief of Staff.
Please do continue.
Yes, sir.
Admiral Bebaus is currently
stationed in the Aptic region.
Admiral Mulusufa is
assembling his fleets
in the direction of
the Mystel System.
Our main fleet will head
into action as soon
as we've received
confirmation of what
the enemy's movements are.
Are you sure we have to wait
and see what the enemy's
going to do in this situation?
Yes, but the key to our
success is how fast
can we read their movements?
Whatever they do, there's
going to be a show-down here.
And we have to win,
otherwise the whole operation
is in danger of collapsing.
In that case we need
to get reinforcements.
We can use reconnaissance ships
from any of the nearby gates
to add to our strength.
Our reconnaissance
missions in Wimpel
and Miofrantia will
prove to be the key
to the entire operation.
Wouldn't you agree,
Chief of Staff?
[JINTO]
And so, because we belonged
to the Latouche Squadron,
First Division
of the 1058th Battalion,
were sent off on our mission
towards the Wimpel Gate.
Luckily, we were the first ones
to discover the enemy ships.
Unluckily, that also
meant we were the first
to enter into battle.
[SOBAASH] All mines have
been confirmed destroyed.
All enemy space-time bubbles
have been eliminated.
[sighs]
[sighs] Well, I guess they
finally ran out of things
to throw at us.
Damage report?
There's a breach in
the hull at the back,
on the port side.
I think we'll be okay--
it doesn't look serious.
Captain, we've received a
message from Command HQ.
Go ahead and read it.
[EKURYUA]
The enemy's front line has been
successfully eliminated.
Withdraw immediately.
Withdraw? Even though we won?
Our mission was
to find the enemy,
not to secure the
Wimpel Planetary System.
I guess so.
The message also says
that the main fleet
of the enemy is advancing.
Understood. Prepare to withdraw!
Captain! Our space-time
bubble is starting to slow--
[GAMROIL 2nd OFFICER]
They report a decrease in speed
due to the debris
collected from the enemy
in their space-time bubbles.
Understood.
Send them this reply:
I give permission for the
Basroil and the Seigroil
to fall behind our squadron.
And we will pray
for their safe return.
[GAMROIL 2nd OFFICER]
Roger. Sending reply now!
[sighs]
[SOBAASH]
Captain...
Huh?
[SOBAASH] It's been quite
a while since you took a break,
hasn't it?
I'll take over the watch.
You should go get some rest.
Yes, thank you.
I accept your offer.
But I want everyone else
to get some rest as well.
Hey, what are you doin'?
You can't go in there!
Diaho! Huh?
[JINTO]
Come on, don't bother her, okay?
Sleep well, Captain.
[JINTO yelps]
Huh?
Enemy attack?!
Is it a direct hit?!
Give me a report
on the situation!
[SOBAASH] We're checking
right now, Captain!
[JINTO]
What happened?
I don't know.
All right, I'm coming!
Jinto!
Huh?
Thanks a lot.
That's okay! You
weren't that heavy!
[LAFIEL]
Fool!
[SOBAASH] We've got to
stabilize the pressure
on the ship!
I'm already working on it!
But the space-time bubble
generator is more important!
I agree. Second Aviator!
What about the Seigroil?
They're still with us.
I'm trying to establish
a connection now.
[LAFIEL]
I gather this is an emergency.
I'm gonna need an
accurate report from you
as quickly as you can!
There's been a mine
attack, Captain.
A mine attack?!
Please go on.
[SOBAASH] We destroyed them
with the laser cannon.
However, the mines
came in pretty close,
and several pieces of
shrapnel hit the ship.
The same thing happened
to the Seigroil .
[LAFIEL]
Is there any damage?
We're still in the process
of checking it out.
We suffered a pressure leak
in at least 16 places.
And some equipment's
been damaged.
And as for the rest,
it's hard to say right now.
Supply Officer, work with the
Line Wing Aviator to discover
exactly what damage
has been inflicted.
[JINTO]
Yes, Captain.
I still can't believe
how all those
mines were activated
at the same time.
At the same time?
There were three
aimed at us and four
aimed at the Seigroil and
they were all activated
within two seconds
of each other.
Doesn't sound like
it happened by chance.
No.
Captain! We've made
contact with the Seigroil .
They're coming through now.
Deca-Commander Abriel,
we have a serious situation
here on the Siegroil .
--[gasps]
--What's it like with you?
We appear to have suffered
some extensive damage,
but we're not sure of
the repercussions yet.
[SAMSON]
Captain...
Things don't look too good here.
The space-time
bubble communicator
and the radar system
are badly damaged.
A lot of other
equipment is out, too,
but those are
the worst affected.
We should count ourselves lucky
there were no
fatalities on board.
[RAGASH]
Hmm...
Sounds like you're
in pretty much
the same situation as us.
[LAFIEL]
It's that bad?
[RAGASH]
I'm afraid so.
We were in the same
area when the attack
was launched, so it's not
surprising that we both got hit.
And now it looks as though
we're stranded in Plane Space.
[LAFIEL] Stranded...
and we're right in front
of the approaching enemy fleet.
[SAMSON] Repairs to
stabilize the pressure
on board have been completed.
[LAFIEL]
Good work.
What about the space-time
bubble communicator?
We've got an idea about that.
Given the materials
we have on board,
we believe that to
attempt any repairs
would be a waste of time.
You're kidding!
We just received word
from the Seigroil
a minute ago.
Their space-time
bubble communicator
and radar system
are beyond repair.
[SAMSON]
So...
I guess we came out of this
slightly better than them.
Then does that mean our
radar system can be fixed?
It'll take about six
hours to do the work.
[LAFIEL]
Very well.
I suppose the only
thing we can do now
is sit here and wait.
[EKURYUA]
Transmission from the Seigroil !
They're requesting that we keep
the space-time
bubble stationary.
[LAFIEL]
Understood.
[SOBAASH]
At the moment we can't even tell
which direction the
space-time bubble is heading.
[JINTO] And what's worse,
for the next six hours,
we won't be able to tell
if there's an enemy
space-time bubble approaching!
Deca-Commander Abriel!
How are things going with you?
The emergency repairs
on our radar system
have now been completed.
But to be honest,
I can't say that
things are looking much
brighter than before.
[SOBAASH]
Although the radar's working,
its quality has deteriorated.
We can only detect objects
that are in close proximity.
[LAFIEL] But at the moment,
we haven't picked up
anything within our range.
[RAGASH] We can't just randomly
move around in the dark.
Even if our allies send
a ship out to rescue us,
there's still one big
hurdle to overcome.
[JINTO] While we waited,
everyone's nerves
were on edge as never before.
And this tension lasted
for over 40 hours.
[JINTO] Space-time bubbles
move around in Plane Space
a bit like a ball which has
fallen onto the floor.
When the ball is rolling,
its impetus causes it to travel.
But when it stops rolling,
it continues to spin
in one position.
In the same way,
although we had stopped,
the space-time bubble
continued to spin
and the generator was using up
precious anti-matter fuel.
To conserve that fuel,
we had to make
some sacrifices in
how we went about
our lives aboard the ship.
Eventually, there was
a change in the situation.
Captain!
The radar's picked up
something heading towards us.
How big is it?
[EKURYUA] It looks like
it could be a squadron.
Get a message to the
Seigroil immediately.
There're some space-time
bubbles heading this way?!
[RAGASH] Our fuel is only going
to last about six hours.
How about you, Basroil ?
I think we can survive
for about ten hours more.
I don't get what's goin' on.
We're calculating
how long we've got
if we decide to escape using
our remaining anti-matter fuel.
Escape? But what for?
Since our space-time
bubble communicator
is out of action,
we're not in a position
to tell if those bubbles
heading towards us
contain enemy ships or allies.
No way!
[RAGASH] I realize it's
a simple calculation,
but if we combine fuel
from the two ships,
we'll have 16 hours' worth.
[LAFIEL]
Is that all?
[SAMSON] It's okay,
we've got plenty of time.
Don't rush it, guys!
It would take a man
with more courage
than I to drop one of those
anti-matter fuel containers.
[SOBAASH] Transfer their
fuel and their crew
onto our ship and then separate?
It is a logical course
of action to take.
If we leave the Seigroil and all
the debris it collected behind,
we can increase our
speed significantly.
But isn't it risky?
Working manually inside
a space-time bubble?
There's still a lot of
debris scattered about.
Even with a Calike this
would've been a difficult
job to pull off.
Hello, Captain?
We have successfully
transferred both the fuel
and the crew of the
Seigroil onto the Basroil !
So, Captain Ragash,
you heard the news.
You should come on board now.
I'm afraid that I
and my officers
are not in a position
to accept your offer,
Deca-Commander Abriel...
What?! Why not?!
I'm sorry I didn't tell
you this earlier, but...
The damage to the ship
means there's no way
we can escape from
the bridge here.
There were many
other areas on board
which required more
immediate attention.
This part of the ship
took a low priority.
Unfortunately, we haven't
had the time or the manpower
to create an escape
route for ourselves.
But my honor would not permit me
to leave you out
here in Plane Space
without any fuel
or hope of rescue!
This isn't about your
own personal honor
or feelings about the
situation, Your Highness!
In the same way
that you, as a princess,
have responsibilities
and duties to your subjects,
I, as an officer
of the Star Forces,
am responsible for my crew.
But, Captain, you...
By choosing this
course of action,
I have decided to save the lives
of as many of my
crew as possible.
That is honorable.
Is that not right?
[RAGASH]
Deca-Commander Abriel!
I entrust my crew to your care.
Promise you'll take
care of them.
[LAFIEL]
I promise.
I'm going to end
the transmission now.
Over and out.
[gasps]
The connections
between the ships
have been released.
[SOBAASH]
The Seigroil is drifting away.
[SOBAASH] Captain,
what are your orders now?
Begin... separation.
Yes, Captain.
[JINTO] When the Basroil
separated from space-time fusion
we had to leave the Siegroil ,
and those left on the ship,
behind us.
With no fuel left,
the Seigroil couldn't avoid
coming into the path of the
advancing space-time bubbles.
They had become a decoy.
Giving their lives so
that we could escape.
And then...
The Seigroil is gone.
The ship and the people
that were left on board
will be transformed
into space-time particles
and float around
Plane Space for eternity.
[KRAN] Ugh. It's getting kind of
hard to breathe in here.
They're cutting back
on everything
to try and save fuel--
probably even the air supply!
[KRAN] And exactly how
much fuel do you think
we're gonna save by doing that?!
Five minutes?
Ten minutes, maybe?!
[PAVERYUA]
How the hell should I know?
Damn! Why don't we
simply surrender
to whoever's chasing us
in those bubbles?
So, a prisoner of war
camp or being
stuck in Plane Space...
both sound very appealing.
[LAFIEL]
No. I cannot permit it.
I should've known
I'd get a response
like that from you.
Captain, more than half
of the members of the crew
have said they
want to surrender!
Even if it's the enemy
in those space-time bubbles,
if we run out of fuel, the
alternative is just as bad!
It hasn't happened yet.
We'll continue to
retreat until we're left
with no choice.
[SAMSON sighs]
I think everybody's
reached their limit.
I expect their nerves'll run
out long before the fuel does!
[LAFIEL] It's my duty to try
and bring everyone back alive.
There's another group
of space-time bubbles
ahead of us.
Looks like it's the size
of one squadron.
From the front.
So, Captain, what do
you want us to do?
Captain?
Those space-time bubbles
are our allies.
I'm sure of it.
We must continue to advance!
I, uh... Yes, Captain!
Captain!
A small space-time bubble
has been released
from the lead ship!
I think it's probably a mine!
A mine?!
I hope not.
We can't dodge it
at this distance.
We don't have enough power
to fire the laser cannon!
I don't care.
Continue to advance
on the current course.
Ten seconds until
space-time fusion!
Eight...
Seven...
Six...
Five...
Four...
Three...
Two...
One.
Space-time fusion!
[EKURYUA] The self-destruct
system isn't responding!
[JINTO] Hold on--the mine's
going right past...!
It missed us!
[GAMROIL 2nd OFFICER]
This is the Star Force
Defense Fleet of the Aptic Gate.
This is a message for
our fellow attack ship.
Immediately enter
into space-time fusion
with the lead ship!
I repeat: This is the
Imperial Star Force...
We're receiving a
transmission? But how?
[LAFIEL]
That's simple.
The transmission isn't
coming from another
space-time bubble.
Then where would
it be coming from?
[LAFIEL]
What we thought was a mine
was a transmitter containing
a message for us.
There's only one person
who would think of this...
My bet is it's Unit
Commander Atosuryua!
[SOBAASH]
In that case...
[LAFIEL]
You heard the message!
Hurry up with the
space-time fusion!
[SOBAASH]
Yes, Captain!
[EKURYUA] The Gamroil is
trying to get through!
Uploading the connection now!
Welcome back to
the fleet, Basroil .
I can't tell you how good it
is to have you with us again.
Thank you very much, ma'am.
I'll report on the last moments
of the Siegroil later on.
[ATOSURYUA]
Those space-time bubbles
that are chasing you
are from the fleet
of the United Mankind.
We will eliminate them
and then retreat.
Roger!
[JINTO sighs]
We were saved!
Saved from certain death...
[SAMSON]
Whew!
Can you imagine what
would have happened
if we'd surrendered
to those guys?
Doesn't bear thinkin' about!
But, Captain, what I wanna
know is how you knew
those space-time
bubbles ahead of us
were gonna be our ships?
[SOBAASH]
Yes, I'd like to know that, too.
What evidence did you
have available to you
to make such a decision?
That's a... a military secret!
[JINTO]
It was all intuition!
How dare you be so rude to me!
I just wasn't certain,
that's all.
Time was running out for us.
We'd have run out of
fuel sooner or later.
I had to make a decision
one way or the other,
so I went with my intuition.
But, you seemed so confident
we were doing the right thing!
The captain has to act like that
to instill confidence
in the crew
in these kinds of situations.
Don't you remember?
Someone once said to me:
"when unsure whether
you should stop or go,
you should go."
Ya know something?
If that's all it was...
[laughs]
Jinto! I don't see
what's so funny.
It's just that maybe
we should keep this
a secret from everybody.
I mean, if they found out...
I don't know... and...
[laughs]
[DUSANYU]
So the main forces of the enemy
have moved into Wimpel?
[KENESH]
Yes.
The reconnaissance ships
in the Aptic region
have confirmed the information.
[DUSANYU] In that case,
we can assume that Aptic
is going to be the main
target of the enemy assault.
[SAMSON]
You seriously think she's calm?!
[SOBAASH] Far more than
I thought she would be.
Maybe she feels a bit
out of place here.
And she's probably
finding it difficult,
having superiors
ordering her around,
given her background.
A toast!
[SOBAASH] I think they
either need to give her
more power to be used
at her discretion,
or it might be better
if she just acted alone.
Feels a bit out of place here...
I remember some kid sayin'
something along those lines.