[meows]
[LAFIEL]
Diaho! What is it with you?!
You're supposed to be
Jinto's cat, not mine!
Faithfulness obviously isn't
one of your strong points!
Jinto, can't you stop your
cat wandering in here?
Sorry, Lafiel.
He hasn't been giving you
any trouble, has he?
[LAFIEL] I can understand
you wanting to have a pet
when we're on patrol and
have lots of free time.
But we're going
into battle soon!
And you're not going to
have time to look after him.
And he's going
to get in the way.
Don't you think
it's unfair to him?
It's okay, don't worry.
If we have to evacuate the ship,
I'll make sure to take
Diaho with me when I go.
Don't say that--
you're tempting fate!
Anyway, that's not what I mean.
It's unfair to the cat because
it's kind of an artificial life
up here--no mice to catch,
none of the things a
normal cat should have.
There's nothing
I can do about that.
The Basroil's my home.
There's nowhere else
for Diaho to go.
There's nothing to stop you
leaving him with somebody else.
There's no regulation against
having a cat on board.
Common sense dictates
it's not a good idea.
You're not taking
this seriously--
he should leave the ship.
But, hold on--I thought the Abh
used to go into battle with
their children on board!
A cat's no big deal.
[LAFIEL] Yes, but those were
special circumstances.
We had to be ready to move
at a moment's notice.
We're not in that
situation. At least...
Not yet.
Oh, well, all right.
If I get a chance, I'll take
him back to Lakfakalle.
Not that I can think of anyone
who could look after him.
Everyone I knew from
Officer Training School
is away fighting.
If you want me to intervene
with the royal family
on your behalf, then why
don't you just say so?
[JINTO]
Thanks! That'd be great!
To be honest, I was
hoping you'd say that.
Come on, Diaho.
[meows]
[JINTO]
Let's get outta here.
Looks like you're
not welcome anymore.
You stupid...
[JINTO]
Well, Diaho, it's been a while
since you went home.
Three whole years. A lot
can happen in that time.
[JINTO] Three years ago,
I got the chance to see
where Lafiel was from
for the first time.
A place filled
with glowing light,
a place where the stars meet.
[JINTO] But the only
light ahead of us now
was the light of battle
and it was starting to shine
brighter and brighter.
[NARRATOR speaking Baronh]
The enemy's main mobile
command fortress
will be within firing
range in 30 seconds!
All ships prepare to
concentrate your fire
on the second sector
of the enemy lines.
[CREW 2B]
All ships standing by!
[CREW 2C]
Target fire on the second sector
of the enemy ship! Fire!
[ENEMY CREW screams]
[CREW 2A] Enemy guard ships
have been destroyed!
[CREW 2B] Prepare to fire
the electro-magnetic cannon!
[CREW 2C] The electro-magnetic
cannon is ready to fire!
[CREW 2B]
Fire!
[CREW 2D] We have been
ordered by the commander
to retreat from the enemy's
mobile command fortress.
Set the ship on a
course of 150 degrees
and follow the Lashkau .
[sighs] This is so tedious.
Huh?
[SPOOR] They must've known
they were gonna lose
if we beat them that easily.
Why didn't they just run away
while they had the chance?
[KUFADIS] Well, Admiral
Spoor, I expect they
simply miscalculated our speed.
It looks as though
most of the enemy
did manage to escape
before we arrived.
They're probably waiting
for an opportunity
to counterattack.
Will you please refrain
from telling me
things that I already know?
If you carry on this rate,
I'm going to die of boredom.
Excuse me, Commander!
The President of
the Aptic System
would like to talk with you.
[3rd FLEET COMM. CHIEF]
Message coming through
from Admiral Spoor
of the First Fleet!
[KENESH]
Let's hear it then.
[CREW 2D] The First Fleet
has successfully demolished
the enemy's mobile
command fortress
within the Aptic System.
Full details are available
in the report which can be
sent to you immediately.
Very well then.
As soon as the communication
link is ready, send the file.
I do not expect there to be
any changes to the plans,
but wait until you receive
confirmation before proceeding.
Understood!
Looks like we came out
of that rather well.
No damage to the fleet at all.
[KENESH]
I presume we may now continue
with our plan to have
Admiral Spoor's Fleet advance
and capture the
enemy's major gates,
starting with Miskel,
Dalmav and Demetel.
The attack will then
be sustained in order
to capture further gates.
The Third Fleet
and the Fifth Fleet
will follow Admiral Spoor's
route in order to set up
a main supply line.
[KENESH]
While this is happening,
the Second and Fourth
Fleets will advance
from both sides in a pincer
movement and capture
any inhabited star systems
in order to strengthen
the defensive line.
[DOSANYU] Excellent. By cutting
through enemy territory,
we should be able to reach
our allies on the other side.
But speed is of the essence.
We've received the report from
the communication ship, sir.
I'll display it now.
Here you go.
How far can we advance before
the enemy strikes back?
How far?
[TALAS] Recent events have
made it clear that our fleet
isn't powerful enough to
challenge your control of space.
However, I hereby pledge
that we shall continue
to combat all ruthless
invaders until you
leave us alone!
[TALAS] As president
of the United Mankind,
I believe it is my duty
to undertake this challenge.
We shall not flag or fail.
We shall fight on the beaches,
we shall fight in the fields
and in the streets,
we shall fight in the hills.
We will never surrender!
Then I hope you do your best.
Huh? What?
But...?!
[sighs] That was the
most boring thing
I've had to do all day.
There's nothing worse than
a dull but well-meaning
president attempting to speak
passionately about his planet.
Chief!
Huh?
While I was wasting
my time listening
to that fool drone on, anything
happen I should know about?
Yes.
We have successfully
managed to take over
the area of space
around Aptic III.
We have seized 79
percent of the enemy's
anti-substance fuel
production facilities
around the Aptic star.
This means that our own mobile
anti-substance fuel-production
factories are now
62 percent complete.
Our plan to set up
an operations base
on Aptic IV, complete with
a supply depot for solid fuel
and propellant extract, is now
about 17 percent complete.
We estimate that getting
the operations center up
and running will take the
greatest amount of time,
but in approximately
218 hours...
So basically, everything is
going according to plan, yes?
Uh... Yes?
[SPOOR] So next time,
do me a favor and just say
there's no change when
there's no change, got it?
How long have you been
doing this anyway?
Don't you think it's
about time you learned
to give more concise answers?
Of course, I understand.
I'll try to be more careful.
[SPOOR] This is very
boring, isn't it, Chief?
[KUFADIS] Jeez, what does
the admiral want from me?
[SPOOR]
Communications Chief!
I want you to call
Rosesh for me.
Yes, ma'am!
[SPOOR]
Commander!
How are the preparations
for departure going?
Perfectly, Commander in Chief!
Hear that? Nice and concise.
That was a perfect
response, dear Chief!
[sighs]
Let's prepare to
depart immediately!
Yes!
We'll send the scout
ship squadron Dikspa
to the Miskel system
to search the regions there
in accordance with our plans.
[sighs]
I am so, so bored!
[SAMSON] Here's a toast
to the beloved blue earth!
Samson, you should have
got off the ship
and gone for a visit.
Ah, that's good!
No. No way I could do that.
But why not?
Officers who head down there
are usually given the cold
shoulder by the regular crew.
They think we're
gonna put a damper
on them having a good time.
[SAMSON]
At least, that's how I felt
before I became an officer.
I remember giving
them some real grief
for intruding on our--
er--"activities"!
Now that the positions
are reversed,
I couldn't possibly
spoil their fun.
[JINTO] In that case, I guess
there's not much point
in me going down there then?
[SAMSON laughs]
Yeah, you being a
member of the nobility
as well as an officer...
You probably wouldn't
be too popular!
But it's all an
experience, right?
Waiter!
I mean, if you really
want to go down
to the planet, I won't stop you.
That's okay.
Don't worry about it.
I've had plenty of experiences
like that already.
[SAMSON]
Huh? That's too bad.
Are ya sure you don't wanna go?
Yeah, I'm sure.
You know, the thing
I miss most is nature.
Cheers.
When you're up here in space,
well, sure you can have a drink,
but you don't get the chance
to appreciate nature
in the same way.
You know, sometimes,
I regret becoming an officer.
The president of the
Aptic System is trying
to get through to us again!
What does he want
to say to us now?
I don't wanna hear his
grumbling and complaining.
I think it was a bit more
serious than a complaint.
Really? Then what was it?
I've got an idea.
Why don't you take my place
and listen to what that bumbling
fool has to say this time?
Tell him I'm far
too busy right now.
[laughs] Very well, Admiral.
Transfer the call to me.
It's coming through now.
[KUFADIS]
Good day, Mr. President.
The commander in chief is
currently occupied elsewhere.
I have the honor of accepting
your message on her behalf.
[TALAS]
What is your rank?
I'm the chief of staff.
My name is Kufadis, sir.
The chief of staff?
Then you're just the man.
Before I speak with your
commander in chief again,
there's an issue I think I need
to bring to your attention.
I hope you don't mind.
[KUFADIS]
Of course not--what is it?
[TALAS] Well, I believe there
must be some sort of fault
with your communication system.
[KUFADIS]
As far as we're aware,
everything is working perfectly.
[TALAS]
But that's strange.
I thought I gave you
a very clear message
that we intend to fight
to the bitter end.
[KUFADIS] Yes. I do
recall hearing something
along those lines.
[TALAS]
Well then, I wonder if it's our
communication system that
isn't working properly.
You see, I could be wrong,
but I'm positive I heard
your commander in chief
encourage us.
[KUFADIS]
Yes, sir, that is correct.
Huh?! I'm puzzled.
I declare our
intention to fight,
Then your commander
in chief, our enemy,
decides that she wants
to encourage us?
It doesn't make any sense!
Yes, I see what you mean.
[TALAS] I thought I'd
done my best to cultivate
an understanding of the Abh
culture and way of life
so that I could communicate
effectively with you.
But obviously, it
wasn't good enough.
I don't understand it at all!
So, tell us why you
became an Abh, then.
Huh? An Abh? Me?
Well, let's see...
Once I'd become an officer,
the next step to
becoming a member
of the elite class
was to become an Abh.
I like all the privileges
that go with being
part of that crowd!
But in the long run,
all I really wanna do
is go back home and retire.
Maybe do some farming.
But why did you enter
the Imperial Fleet
in the first place?
I dreamt of going into space.
Joining the Fleet was a way
of fulfilling the dream.
Once I got up here,
I realized that
it wasn't really what
I wanted out of life.
I mean, it's all very
nice and everything,
but knowing how to
operate a spaceship
isn't a lot of help to
you down on the planet.
So I decided to become an
officer, make as much money
as I could, as fast as I could,
and save up to buy
myself a little farm.
[JINTO] So does that mean
you're gonna retire soon?
No, not yet.
According to my calculations,
I need to take part in
a couple more battles
before I have enough
money saved up.
Gotta keep working till then!
What kind of calculations?
Well, it's not just the money.
The time's gotta be right.
I'm not ready for
retirement just yet.
I'm not sure how much
you know about us,
Mr. President, but like
every race, you will find
a lot of variety and
differences between us.
Most of us, myself included,
would find it unusual
to offer our enemies
any kind of encouragement.
[TALAS]
Hold on just a minute!
Are you trying to tell me that
your commander in chief is...
How shall I put this--
are you trying to tell me
that she's not normal? Well?
Choose your words carefully.
Oh, yes, my appologies.
So if you were in her place,
what would your
response have been?
I'd probably tell you
to do as you like...
...for as long as you could.
[TALAS sighs]
I'm afraid that's no better.
Where did you say your
home planet was again?
Ah, yes.
Ah... Midgrad.
You'd probably know it by
its Abh name: Planet Dakufo.
Heard of it?
[JINTO]
Sorry, no.
[SAMSON laughs]
That's disappointing!
I have to admit that
it's not very well known,
but we do have a place
in the history books.
We learned how to travel in
space before the empire did!
Whoa!
In the past, our
planet had to decide
between belonging
to the United Mankind
or to the Human Empire Abh.
To cut a long story short,
we pledged allegiance
to the empire.
What made you decide
to go with them?
[sighs] Well, if
you must know...
Our eating habits are,
well, quite unique.
Outsiders are sometimes taken
aback by the things we eat.
Before we pledged
allegiance to one nation,
some people from the United
Mankind talked to our leaders
and tried to get us to
change our eating habits.
On the other hand, the Abh
didn't say anything
about how we ate.
Or at least, not in front of us.
That was probably what swung
things in their favor.
Then we figured that
if they'd let us eat
what we've always eaten,
we could compromise
and let them call
Mid Grad by another name.
So now it's Planet Dakufo--
to the Abh at least!
So that's the story
of how we came
to be with the empire!
So what do you eat?
[SAMSON]
Mm... You don't wanna know.
I've lost too many
friends this way
and I don't wanna lose another.
But I'm not your friend--
I just work with you.
[JINTO, SAMSON]
Hm?
That's pretty blunt--
you Abhs certainly
don't worry about holding back!
[JINTO chuckles]
Why are you so surprised?
You've been an Abh
for way longer than me!
I only became one three
years ago, remember?
Sorry, did I insult you?
Nah, you're okay.
[SPOOR]
Hm. This is interesting!
The president wanted me
to reply to his challenge
with some sort of
official counter-challenge?
A summons to surrender?
Yes.
Standing up and pledging
to fight to the end
against an invading force
is a very attractive way
to win votes.
[TALAS]
You see,
when I used the term
"ruthless invaders,"
I was just trying to make it
more appealing to the voters.
Nothing more, no offense meant.
[KUFADIS] The president
also asked if you could
spice up the summons to
surrender with some insults,
racial slurs,
that sort of thing.
Well, well, well!
This gets more interesting
by the minute!
Although it's a shame he
didn't tell me about it
straight away, instead
of making me think
he actually believed
his own bluster.
Who knows?
I might actually have gone
along with such a crazy idea!
Huh?
Besides, His Imperial Highness,
the commander in chief,
will be here soon.
I have to leave
all that official
"demand for surrender" stuff
to him--you know he loves
every minute of it!
Did you ever hear what
he told the Hyde System
when they had to relinquish
their sovereignty?
[KUFADIS]
No, I don't think I did.
[SPOOR]
He was actually very impressive.
Considering he's an Abriel,
it was very high-handed,
nicely sarcastic,
and extremely effective.
You should know that the task
of governing your world...
...is not a priority for us.
In fact, it is far from elegant.
[SPOOR] If it was me,
I'm sure that I could have
put it much more elegantly.
Oh, and by the way, Chief...
Yes? What do you want?
[SPOOR] The president wants
us to use something
called "racial slurs"?
[KUFADIS]
Hm? Yes.
Yes, phrases like:
"you lousy land-loving pig!"
or "bunch of crawling,
slack-jawed mud turtles!"
Oh, I understand now. Well...
They're a little bit old
fashioned but there's something
about them, don't you think?
[KUFADIS] She's not seriously
thinking of using them?
[DIAHO meows]
You can stop your
whining, Diaho.
I'm not gonna let you out--
not with all these squirrels
around to tempt you!
[DIAHO meows]
[JINTO]
When I say "no" I mean "no"!
[DIAHO meows]
Jinto! How come you
brought your cat?
[JINTO] Well, I couldn't leave
him on board the Basroil .
There was nobody left
there to look after him!
[EKURYUA]
But he hasn't been with you!
Did he get a little
vacation as well?
He was looked after.
I took him to a place where
there were lots of other cats
staying and lots of mice
to chase and catch.
Think he had fun?
I think so.
But the captain told me
I had to send him
back home to Lakfakalle.
Why'd she do that?
She didn't think havin'
a cat on board the ship
was very appropriate--especially
if we're heading into battle.
So now I've gotta say
goodbye to Diaho.
I'll be sorry to see him go.
I've kind of got used to having
him around all the time.
He's pretty cute, for a cat.
Hey, be careful!
Watch what you're sayin'
in front of him, will ya?
We don't want him
to get a big head!
I thought all cats
had big heads,
not just Diaho!
What a profound
insight that is.
[SAMSON]
Captain?!
[LAFIEL] We've finally been
assigned to a squadron.
We're going to be flying with
the Battleship
Squadron Latouche,
as part of the First Division
of the 1058th Battalion.
We'll be leaving
in about 12 hours.
[SAMSON] If you ask me, that
seems just a little bit hasty.
[LAFIEL]
I agree.
But it's supposedly
part of our training.
[EKURYUA] Do you know
what happens after this?
[SOBAASH]
It looks like we'll be heading
to a different system.
[EKURYUA]
Which one?
[SOBAASH] They haven't given
us any information yet.
I guess we'll just have to wait
until we arrive to find out.
[LAFIEL] There's still two hours
and 18 minutes of leave left
before we have to return.
However, I would
appreciate it if you'd
start preparing to
leave immediately.
Does anyone have
a problem with that?
Not me!
To be honest,
things were gettin'
a bit boring down here anyway.
Very well. Officer Ekuryua,
please get the Calike ready
for transport back to the ship.
We'll be heading
back before you.
Right away!
Let's go!
[JINTO]
Roger!
And what've you got there?
Uh... Don't you recognize him?
This is Diaho, Captain.
[LAFIEL]
I thought I told you to send him
back home to Lakfakalle.
I was gonna do it before
I got back on board.
I'll have to go and make
the arrangements now.
There isn't enough time.
You can bring him with you.
But just this once.
Next time, make sure
you're more organized.
Of course. Thank you, Captain.
Huh! That was rough!
You'd never guess she was
speaking to a fellow officer
from that conversation!
Jinto!
Do you know the name of our new
storm troop squadron commander?
Why do you think I'd know
something like that?
I'll tell you. Her name's
Hecto-Commander Atosuryua.
Atosuryua, yeah?
That seems familiar. Where
would I have heard that before?
C'mon, use your head!
If you have any brains, that is.
Nope. All my brains
have turned to mush.
Sorry about that!
You do know that she's
the younger sister
of Baron Febdash...
Nicely done...
...Your Highness!
Huh?
You know, Your Majesty,
if I didn't know you
better, I'd say that your
behavior is verging
on being incorrigible.
Is that a compliment?
And I have no doubt
that you'll give us
plenty of opportunities
in the future
to reinforce that idea,
given your track record.
Hecto-Commander Atosuryua!
We're not in training anymore--
this is the real thing!
Activate the main engine!
Let's see who arrives first!
We've received a request
from the Gamroil
to perform space-time fusion.
Salute the enemy.