[BLUE DRAGON panting]
[BLUE DRAGON] My eyes.
They ache more than usual today.
Intruders? How'd
they get down here?
That woman's voice.
She's in distress.
He's trying to trap
her underground.
I have to stop him!
[YONA gasps]
[heartbeat]
[DRAGON]
The Four Dragon warriors.
[BLUE DRAGON]
What's happening?
[DRAGON] From this day forward,
you shall act as our avatars.
We have granted you our power
so you may protect
the Crimson Dragon.
It is your duty to defend
him with your lives.
[BLUE DRAGON]
Whose voice am I hearing?
[BLUE DRAGON panting]
[BLUE DRAGON]
My eyes are killing me.
When I touched that young woman,
my blood started rushing
through my veins.
I thought I was
going to collapse.
Then, I heard those voices.
[BLUE DRAGON]
Who was that man?
And why did I feel some sort
of strange bond with him?
The words "white dragon"
kept floating through my mind.
My blood is boiling.
What a strange sensation.
I've never felt
anything like it before.
What's happening to my eyes?
Why are they aching so badly?
I need to try to calm down.
No one must know about my
cursed power. Never again.
Wait, are you telling me
you were almost kidnapped
by one of the villagers?
The nerve! First, they
disrespect the princess,
and then they try to
trap her underground?
Those miserable
plebeians are lucky
I don't rip their faces off!
There's no need to get violent!
[HAK]
Plebeians, huh?
Big word for a small man.
Why don'tcha settle
down, moneybags?
Let a real man handle this.
Neither of you is
"handling" anything, got it?
Anyway, I dunno about this guy
being the Blue Dragon Warrior.
Are you sure he's the one?
Yes.
[HAK]
Then why'd he run away from you?
Who knows?
There's something
strange going on here,
but I can't put my finger on it.
What really
strikes me as odd
is how this village is
the exact opposite of yours.
What?
Then again, maybe it's
just our perception.
It's possible we've
been lead astray.
What if the White Dragon
Warrior's village
is the exception to the rule?
There we were surrounded
by crimson-hair-worshippers
and Gija's power was revered,
but it's different here.
The people of this village
couldn't care less
about the princess's
crimson hair,
and they don't idolize
their warrior.
Instead, they seem to
loathe him and his power.
Maybe that's why he doesn't
want anything to do with us--
[GIJA]
That's nonsense!
It's the Four Dragons' sworn
duty to make their presence know
when their master comes calling!
I didn't hesitate to introduce
myself to the princess
for I knew it was
my job to protect her!
Not everybody can be
as perfect as you.
No, guess not.
That was sarcasm, you know.
[YONA]
You're wrong.
He didn't hesitate. He saved me.
And I could feel
kindness in his touch.
I wanna see him again.
You don't seriously wanna
go back to the caves, do you?
Yeah!
Most folks would stay
far away from the place
after what you went through.
You've sure got guts,
Princess Yona.
[giggles]
Well, let's go.
All we have to do is find that
secret passageway, right?
Shouldn't be too hard.
[YONA gasps]
You should stay here, Princess.
But, Hak.
[HAK]
It's too dangerous.
Yun and I will find
the Blue Dragon Warrior
and bring him to you.
What about me?
I should go, not you!
[HAK] Okay, then I'll stay
and protect the princess.
You fiend!
Head back to the caves and try
and find the secret passageway,
but don't go insi--
[YONA]
No!
Uh.
I'm going. Along with Gija and
Yun. You're staying here, Hak.
[HAK grunts]
[YONA] Gija can sense
the Blue Dragon Warrior
and Yun knows his way
through the caves.
I'm sorry, but this might
be my only chance.
Maybe... I can persuade
him to join us. Please?
Geez.
You seriously want me to stay
out here and be the lookout?
And I suppose I don't have
any say in the matter.
Don't worry, I promise
I'll be careful.
You know the only reason
I'm asking this of you
is because I trust you, right?
[HAK sighs]
It's true.
[HAK grunts]
You'd better come back
without so much as a scratch.
Otherwise...
...you're stuck with me.
I'll be right by your side
for the rest of your life.
Really?
Wow, that sounds annoying!
I'll be extra careful now.
Good. I don't wanna be
stuck with you either.
[YONA giggles]
[YUN]
Poor guy.
[HAK]
Hey, White Snake.
I'm part dragon, not snake-- Uh.
Watch her.
[GIJA]
She's in good hands.
[HAK]
The villagers.
They've been spying
on us the whole time.
You sure are a creepy
bunch, aren't ya?
Look all you want,
you're not getting past me.
Admit it, Princess,
aren't you scared to
venture off like this
without the Lightning Beast?
Of course I am, but I was
trying to play it cool!
I need to learn to
do things myself
so I don't have to
rely on Hak as much.
[YUN]
Did you ever stop to think
that maybe he wants
to be relied on?
[YONA]
You think?
I don't know. I seriously
doubt that's the case
because he swore to serve my
father and his kingdom, not me.
The only reason he's here
is he's following
my father's orders.
I dunno, Princess. I don't
think that's the only reason.
[YONA] He's spent his
entire adult life working
as a general and a bodyguard.
It sounds miserable,
if you ask me.
That's why I hope to give
Hak his freedom back someday.
[YUN]
What?!
This is a dead end! There's
no secret passageway here!
[YONA]
Yes, there is.
[gasps]
[YUN]
Whoa! You're right, it opened!
That's so cool!
[YONA]
Mh-hm.
[YUN]
Hey, Gija, you coming?
[YONA]
Is there something wrong?
[GIJA]
Uh. No.
I can sense the Blue
Dragon's location.
He's straight ahead,
so you two go on.
I'll stay here and wait for you.
What? But we need you.
We'll be fine, Princess.
There's no need to worry,
this beautiful boy
genius knows the way!
[GIJA]
Take care of her.
You know I will.
[GIJA]
Now then.
Would you care to tell me what
business you have with us?
[YEODEOL] No one who goes
through the hidden passageway
can ever leave the caves.
[GIJA]
Is that so?
Are you scoundrels
completely unaware
of the Crimson
Dragon's nobility?
I'm charged with
protecting Princess Yona,
so you'll have to get
past me to get to her.
[BLUE DRAGON]
The White Dragon is nearby.
I can feel it.
And I hear footsteps
coming this way.
[BLUE DRAGON]
Ao, go and hide.
Who are these intruders?
[BLUE DRAGON] If they're
enemies, I'll take them down!
[heartbeat]
We meet again.
[BLUE DRAGON]
Who is she?
Why does she make
me feel this way?
[BLUE DRAGON yelling]
[YUN gasps]
[panting]
This guy is totally crazy!
Then again, what did we expect
from a creep who wears
a mask and hides in caves?
We should get outta here
--while we still can, Princess.
--[AO squeaks]
Well, hello, furry friend.
[YUN]
Huh?
That glutton's got
way too much food
crammed in his pudgy cheeks.
Watch out, he might puke.
So, does this little
guy have a name?
--Ao.
--[YUN] Uh!
[YUN]
I didn't expect him to answer.
I don't think that
suits him at all.
Okay, let's not piss off
the crazy man, Princess!
[BLUE DRAGON]
I suppose she's right.
It doesn't suit him, does it?
But I didn't know
what else to call him.
I'm Princess Yona.
May I ask your name?
Blue... Dragon.
No, that can't
possibly be right.
[BLUE DRAGON grunts]
I mean, that's your title,
but what's your name?
Don't have... one.
I'm just... Blue Dragon.
Stay away!
Who are you people? And why
did you come to this village?
No one has ever come near me
but you and your
white dragon friend.
We're allies.
We mean you no harm,
we've come to speak to you.
[BLUE DRAGON] What is this
feeling that's come over me?
Please, sir.
I need you to
lend me your power.
Won't you come on
this journey with me?
[BLUE DRAGON]
It feels as if I've been waiting
all my life to find her.
You say you need... my power?
[heart beating]
[groans]
[gasps]
Let go of her!
Enemy.
I was told that those who
seek the Blue Dragon's power
are the enemy!
[DRAGON]
The Four Dragon Warriors.
From this day forward,
you shall act as our avatars.
I don't know you.
But I feel as if I should.
Why is my hand
shaking like a leaf?
I thought you were the
enemy, but you're not.
So, who are you?
[BLUE DRAGON] Why do I
feel like I want to cry?
I'm sorry.
It was never my intention
to upset you like this.
I've come here because
my life is in grave danger,
and I need the power of
the Four Dragons to survive.
Will you join me and
become my comrade?
[BLUE DRAGON]
She wants to be... my comrade?
It isn't meant to be.
[BLUE DRAGON] I'm sorry,
I can't do that. I'm cursed.
What do you mean?
My power's dangerous.
It's far too destructive
to ever be used for good.
It must be kept secret.
What nonsense.
Who told you that?
[BLUE DRAGON]
It's the truth.
[YONA] But it's not true,
it's what you've been told.
Please, come with us.
[BLUE DRAGON]
Leave.
Leave me!
Let's go, Princess.
[YONA sighs]
[YONA]
One last thing before I go.
When you grabbed my hand...
I felt your kindness.
[gasps]
[YONA] I don't know why
you believe you're cursed
because I've never felt more
at ease than I did by your side.
You saved me. I wouldn't be
alive if it weren't for you.
For that, I will
always be grateful.
[BLUE DRAGON]
She's leaving.
Uh.
[groaning]
[BLUE DRAGON]
Why does it feel as though
my heart is being ripped out?
[YONA] Will you join me
and become my comrade?
[BLUE DRAGON]
A comrade...
Ao... all that
I want... is a friend.
[BLUE DRAGON]
How could I forget?
All I ever wanted was a friend.
[YUN]
Um, Princess.
Judging by the look on your
face, you're not too happy.
[YONA growling]
It must be miserable
having to live like that.
He didn't have anything,
not even food.
Why does this hurt?
It almost feels as though
I'm abandoning someone
who's important to me.
I just met him.
Why am I so worried about him?
[GIJA] Stay back, cretins!
I'm warning you!
What's wrong?
[YONA gasps]
[YEODEOL]
There they are.
[MAN B]
We must fulfill our duty!
[MAN C]
Kill the intruders!
We'll protect you, Princess.
What's with these guys?
[GIJA]
They want to kill us
so the Blue Dragon Warrior's
identity remains a secret.
They want... to kill us?
[YEODEOL]
Now that you've ventured
into the Blue Dragon's lair,
we cannot allow you
to leave with your lives!
But why? Please, tell me.
Why do you insist on
keeping his identity a secret?
I'm not sure why
but the villagers think
the dragon's noble
power is a curse.
You ignorant fools should be
worshipping him, not hiding him.
[YEODEOL]
Why, you--!
No, I'm far too young
and pretty to die!
[YEODEOL grunting]
[MEN gasp]
That was harsh!
I'm sorry, Princess!
I meant to punch him with
my human hand, I swear!
[YUN]
Yeah, right. You've been itching
to use your super-human
strength, you show off.
I beg you. Tell me.
What do the people
of your village
have against the
Blue Dragon Warrior?
I don't understand why
you think he's cursed.
[MAN B]
That's none of your business!
--[rumbling]
--[ALL gasp]
An Earthquake!
[YEODEOL]
Run!
[ALL yelping]
[YUN whimpering]
Careful, Princess!
[YONA]
Hak!
[HAK]
Uh.
An earthquake?
[MAN C]
We're all gonna die!
Princess!
[HAK] They must be all the way
towards the back of the cave.
Damn it! Uh!
[HAK grunts]
[gasps]
Oh, no. This is bad.
They're trapped.
[HAK]
Princess! Yun! White Snake!
You know the only reason
I'm asking this of you
is because I trust you, right?
[HAK grunts]
[HAK]
This is all my fault.
I never should'a let
her go off without me.
How could I be so stupid?
Now I'm not there to protect
her when she needs me the most.
[HAK]
King Il, if you can hear me...
...please don't take
her from me yet!
[YONA]
Hak.
I'm so scared right now.
More than I've ever been before.
I wanted to prove to you that
I can handle things myself,
that I don't have
to rely on you.
But I'm frightened
without you by my side.
I'm sorry, I don't
wanna give up,
but I feel so incredibly weak.
[GIJA]
Princess?
Wake up!
Princess!
Gija?
How're you feeling?
All right.
It was all such a blur.
At least the
earthquake's over.
[YEODEOL]
It's no good.
The exit's blocked,
we're trapped!
[MAN B] Don't say that!
There's gotta be a way out!
[MAN C]
I dunno...
[YONA]
We're trapped?
[MAN B]
We have to at least try!
Oh, no. We're gonna
die down here.
Yun.
There's only so much
air to go around.
It won't be long before
we're struggling to breathe.
[MAN B]
No, I don't wanna die!
Somebody help us!
[YONA]
This is awful. What'll we do?
I'm so scared.
Where are you, Hak?
[GIJA] It's hard enough
taking this journey with you,
why must you haunt my thoughts?
[gasps]
'Scuse me?
Uh.
Sorry, wasn't talking 'bout you.
Lightning Beast said
something before we left
that keeps echoing in my head.
Watch over her.
Ugh! That jerk already
gets on my last nerve,
hearing his voice floating
around in my brain
just makes it worse!
It's my sworn duty
to protect you, Princess.
Forget about that lazy oaf.
[YONA chuckles]
You're gonna have to
learn to work together.
Fine, I'll give it a try!
Don't be scared, okay?
Hak is on his way.
I just know it.
[HAK grunts]
[HAK]
I'm coming, Princess!
Stay strong!
I promise I'll save you!
[GIJA] We don't have
time to wait for Hak.
We're losing precious
air by the second.
I'm perfectly capable of
getting us out of here myself.
Uh, Gija.
You mind if I ask why
you unwrapped your claws?
To dig!
[GIJA grunts]
[MAN E]
This guy's a monster!
[GIJA]
Shows what you know.
What your village
considers a "curse"
others think of as a "blessing."
It's a shame that
you fear our powers
when they could benefit you.
[MAN G]
Uh! The White Dragon Warrior!
[MAN F] You mean there are
others who've been cursed?
But how can that be?!
I thought the Blue Dragon
was the only one--!
[YEODEOL screaming]
I can't take it anymore!
It's his fault!
None of this
would've happened...
...if it weren't for
the Blue Dragon.
He's the reason we're
going to die in this cave!
Damn it! Get us outta here!
Don't blame him!
We're trapped because
of the earthquake.
He had nothing to do with it!
[YONA]
Why are they scared of him?
He was so gentle and kind.
[MAN B] If you only knew of his
wickedness, you'd understand.
But he's not wicked at all!
You're an outsider!
How would you know?!
[YONA gasps]
[YEODEOL] I'm not sure what we
did to deserve this punishment,
but the dragon-eyed monster
is always born into our clan.
And you wonder why we
think his power is a curse.
Because no matter how many times
we beg the gods for forgiveness,
we are never spared
from this tragedy.
Now, whenever a
Blue Dragon dies,
we live in fear that our child
could become the next one!
[MAN B] We kill all intruders
so the outside world
will never know our clan
bears this horrible curse.
We don't want them
to know our shame.
When the current
Blue Dragon was born,
we immediately put
a mask on his face
and hid him away from the world.
All in the hopes of
protecting our secret.
When he was a boy,
he found his way outside
and used that dreadful power
to kill an entire
army of soldiers.
It was a massacre unlike
any we'd ever seen.
After that happened, we were
forced to move the clan here
because we were afraid
that whoever attacked
might send even more troops.
Haven't we been through enough?!
If this isn't a curse,
then what is?!
[GIJA gasps]
Enough. He's here.
[bells ringing]
[YEODEOL gasps]
[MAN F]
It's him.
[MAN H]
The Blue Dragon Warrior.
[MAN I]
No way.
[YEODEOL] Uhh... I-I wasn't
doing anything wrong, I swear!
The intruders were just asking
us a few questions about you,
that's all!
Stay back!
[YEODEOL gasps]
[YONA] I don't see how anyone
could think his eyes are cursed.
They're so beautiful.
So soulful.
[YONA] And there's
so much sadness in them.
My heart hurts for him.
[BLUE DRAGON] From the very
first moment I saw her,
I knew she would
be my salvation.
She is the light
in the darkness.
Next time on Yona of the Dawn,
Episode 14: "Light."