[STORE OWNER] Go ahead and
make yourselves comfortable.
[YONA] And so began the longest
and darkest night of our lives.
[BOTH yelp]
[YONA] One day remained
before our true battle.
[YONA]
What's going on?
Are we being taken to
the ship? I'm so scared.
And what's the situation
with the latest stock?
[OFFICER A]
All accounted for, Sir.
I was told that two very
attractive units showed up
at the shop late this afternoon.
Apparently one of them
has bright red hair,
which could fetch a high price.
Oh?
Good, I can't wait to
see just how much.
[YONA, YUN gasp]
[YONA]
There are so many of them.
How can these men
get away with this?
Get your asses in there now!
[YUN, YONA yelp]
[YONA yelps]
Hey, what happened?
It looks like you sprained it.
You're gonna have to be extra
careful not to make it worse.
[YONA]
What horrible luck.
I can't let it get in the
way of saving these women.
I'll just have to push
through the pain.
[YONA]
It's him... Yang Keum-ji.
They weren't lying. This looks
like the best batch yet.
My pockets will be lined
with the Kai Empire's money.
[GIRL A] Lord Keum-ji, will we
be taken to our jobs soon?
My family is starving.
I want to get to work
so that I can help them.
Oh, you'll be working all right.
You'll have more jobs than
you could possibly handle.
[gasps]
[KEUM-JI] So, you're the
rare little redhead, then.
You're gonna fetch
me a hefty price...
...if I don't decide
to keep you for myself.
It'd be kinda sad to let
such a pretty face get away.
[YUN]
Yona!
I'd usually pick
money over novelty,
but I've only seen a redhead
like you once before in my life.
I could deal with
less gold to have you.
[YUN]
Lord Keum-ji!
[KEUM-JI]
Huh?
Sir, why don't you
take me instead?
You can make your money on her
and still keep a
beauty for yourself.
What the heck?
What are these words that're
comin' outta my mouth?
Oh yeah?
[YUN]
She's not the one that you want.
I can satisfy you much better.
What's with me?
I don't wanna die!
If he finds out I'm a guy,
he'll rip off what makes me one!
[YUN]
But I promised to protect Yona.
So let him kill me if he wants.
I'd like to let you prove
that to me, sweetheart.
However...
[YUN yelps]
[coughs]
--[GIRLS yelping]
--[YUN groaning]
Don't interrupt me again,
or I'll make it so you
never speak another word.
Lord Keum-ji, be careful
with the product.
[OFFICER A grunts]
--[thud]
--[OFFICER A grunts]
When I say don't interrupt
me, that means you, too.
That's right, shut up
and take it. Ha, ha, ha.
As the product, you're to keep
silent and do exactly as I say,
is that clear?
Take your cues from
little red here, ladies.
[KEUM-JI gasps]
[YONA yelps]
[KEUM-JI]
What the--?
Her eyes... Something in
them shook me to the core.
I wonder...
Redhead, were you born
and raised in Awa's port?
[YONA]
Yes, sir.
I've only ever met
one other person
with crimson hair like
yours in my lifetime.
She was the young daughter
of the late King Il.
I saw her from afar,
but the sun glinting off
her fiery hair drew my eye.
It was the most majestic
thing I'd ever seen.
Her name was Yona.
If I remember correctly,
she'd be about your age.
Surely this can't
be a coincidence.
Are you Princess Yona?
[YUN]
He's found us out.
[YONA]
I'm no princess.
My father is a poor
merchant in Awa.
I came to the store looking for
extra work to support my family.
I've never heard of this
red-haired princess
you speak of.
But, since you think
I look like her,
I could impersonate her and go
by Princess Yona if you'd like.
I wish nothing more than
to bring you joy, my Lord.
[KEUM-JI]
Hm.
Don't you know a joke
when you hear one?
I was obviously
making fun of you.
How could you think
you're like a princess,
groveling in the dirt?
You're clearly a peasant
with no dignity.
Pigs have more
self-respect than that.
Now, pick yourself up.
[KEUM-JI]
What nonsense.
I don't know what
I was thinking.
It's only a coincidence.
Besides, I heard the princess
died when she fled the castle.
No girl who lived her whole life
under the protection of the king
would ever have the power
to shake me, even for a moment.
But this girl has the eyes
of a caged, wild animal.
[chuckles]
[OFFICER A groaning]
[GIRLS sighing]
[YONA]
Yun, are you hurt?
Ugh.
What kinda man would ever
hit a delicate flower like me?
I know.
Your ankle. The swelling's
gotten much worse. Does it hurt?
No, it doesn't.
I forgot about it, actually.
I'm gonna put my
pain to good use.
I'll remember it and
bring it right back to 'im.
Keum-ji is gonna
feel the hurt tenfold.
[GIRL B] I don't understand
what he meant earlier.
A "hefty price"?
Are we going to be sold?
Help me! Get me out
of here right now!
Please come and open the door!
I'm begging you!
I don't wanna...
[GIRL]
It's no use.
No one's gonna save you,
no matter how much you
scream and cry for help.
I've been here for two weeks,
trapped like an animal.
To Keum-ji, we're nothing
more than livestock.
We'll be sold to whoever's
the highest bidder.
It's no surprise. Awa has
always been a corrupt cesspool.
[YONA] And you're content
to accept that, are you?
Accept what?
[YONA]
The corruption.
You could do something.
Save Awa from men like him.
Restore the power to the people
and end the reign of terror that
has plagued you for so long.
[GIRLS gasping]
[GIRL] Ha. There's no way you
are from anywhere around Awa.
Because if you
had grown up here,
you'd know how ridiculous
you sound saying that.
Try to fight. You won't
make it out alive.
You may be right about
me being a foreigner,
but I care about this town.
People I love are fighting for
it now, and we're gonna win.
[GIRLS gasping]
Except we're trapped in a
cellar, facing certain death.
Yeah, we're definitely on
the winning side of this fight.
Why do you always have
to be so sarcastic?
So you really think
there's hope?
Someone might actually
be able to save us?
That's the dumbest
thing you've said yet.
You might think
it's stupid, but still.
If there's any chance
we can be saved,
they'll do it.
You just have to trust me, and
put your life in their hands.
If you wanna make it
out alive, have faith.
[YUN]
Hm.
If we just keep
fighting, we'll survive.
[gasps]
[GIRLS gasping]
[YONA]
I know I have limitations.
At heart, I'm
just a regular girl.
I can't change that, but I can
control how I affect others.
I'm willing to lay down my life
if it'll make the
world a better place.
Please, you have to
help me fight for you.
Together, we can end
this reign of terror.
[JEAHA]
Hak.
Why don't you go
and lie down, huh?
You've been scanning
the harbor since she left--
This is what resting
looks like for me.
Besides, just look
at White Snake.
You should be worried
about that mess.
[JEAHA]
Huh?
--Hey, buddy, lemme take you
--I swear to you!
--to your bunk, okay?
--If he so much as touches her.
[JEAHA]
The heck's that about?
He dozes off for a few minutes.
Then all of a sudden,
he'll jump up
and pick a fight with the air.
Sheesh, that's rough.
He needs to develop some coping
strategies. He looks awful.
You're tired, too.
You need sleep. A lot.
Uh! Why'd you have to go and
whisper creepily in my ear?
Watch it, weirdo!
But it's the truth.
You look tired.
What do you mean?
I look great. At least,
that's what all the ladies
were telling me last night.
As I remember, we
passed out pretty early.
I musta worn 'em
out as usual. Eh?
[JEAHA yelling]
--[HAK] Show us your face.
--[GIJA] Stop hiding from us!
[HAK]
Lemme look at your eyes!
[JEAHA moans]
You've defiled me.
I'm just an object for you
to use and I think I like it.
Clothes on.
You're tired, too!
You don't have to lie!
If you'd stayed up late
with those ladies,
you'd feel the same way.
[SINHA]
I saw you.
You were in the crow's nest
all night, staring at the water.
So, you're stalking me now?
I gotta say.
I'm incredibly flattered, Sinha.
Look, we all know that
you're worried about Yona,
just like the rest of us.
Yeah, of course I am!
We sent the poor kid right
into the belly of the beast.
Waiting is torture. I'm dying
to know whether she's okay.
That's what I wanna hear.
If you care about her
even half as much as I do,
you're okay by me.
You can stand by my side
in battle any day, brother.
Whatever you say.
In any case, what about the
other kid we sent with her?
Yun, right? I'm not so
sure he can handle it.
He seems kinda fragile.
You sure we can trust
him to keep Yona safe?
'Cause I have my doubts.
Don't underestimate Yun.
Yeah.
He isn't just some ordinary
kid. No, not at all.
He's proven himself. I'd trust
him with my life no problem.
[SINHA]
Mm.
[GI-GANG chuckles]
[window howling]
[GI-GANG]
Hm?
Sinha!
[SINHA]
I can see Keum-ji's ships.
They're headed this way.
All right, rascals.
Weapons ready.
This is it.
Tonight we fight what will be
our most important battle ever.
We all know what's at stake.
Let's bring back
Yang Keum-Ji's head!
[PIRATES]
Yeah!
Ao.
[knocking]
Hey! Keep it down in there!
Huh?
So, which one of you is
makin' all the noise? Uh!
[LOOKOUT]
You're gonna pay for that.
How the hell did you
get outta the ropes?
Whaddaya think you're
gonna do with that--?
This!
[GIRL A]
Did you kill him?
[YUN]
No, it's only a sedative,
but he'll be out a while.
For twelve hours at least.
We still need to
act quickly, though.
I can't believe it. You're
actually planning to escape?
What is it? Why are
you trembling?
Your ankle. It looks
pretty awful.
Are you sure you're gonna be
able to go through with this?
If you get caught, you might
get every one of us killed.
Don't worry. We have an
entire army behind us.
Seriously?
Maybe not an army exactly,
but a ship full of allies.
We need to send
them our location.
But how? We sailed out
to sea a while ago.
We're in the middle
of the ocean now.
How do you expect them
to find us out here?
We're going out on the
deck to send up a flare.
[GIRL]
What?
It's a small firework,
but our friends can
see it from miles away.
I've a feeling they're
not too far from here.
Have hope. I promise
we'll save you.
Let's go.
'Kay.
[groaning]
And you're content to
accept that, are you?
Hold on!
The deck is crawling
with Keum-ji's men.
Let me go with
you, I can help.
[BOTH gasp]
[GIRL]
Please, hear me out.
My father's
a shipyard carpenter,
so I grew up around
boats like this one.
I can help you stay hidden.
Thank you so much.
You wanna help? But why?
[GIRL] Because what your friend
said earlier really hit home.
All these years we've
watched our people
be terrorized by Yang Keum-ji.
It's time for us to fight back.
[GIRL]
Are you with me?
My name is Yuri, what's yours?
Oh, my name is... uh... Lina.
And I-- Uh.
My name is Yun. I'm the brains
behind this operation.
I find that hard to believe.
[MERCENARIES yelling]
Sounds like they're here.
Yeah, sure does.
[yelling]
[MERCENARIES grunting]
[MERCENARY F yelling]
[GIJA]
Bring me to Keum-ji!
I'll take his head,
and send the rest to hell!
[HAK]
Hate to break it to you,
but sometimes it's hard
to take you seriously,
--[HAK] White Snake.
--Don't call me White Snake!
Sinha, where's the princess?
I dunno. I can't see her.
[MERCENARY H yelling]
You better go easy on 'em.
You don't want the
old lady throwin' a fit.
I'd watch my tongue
if I were you.
Call the captain old and
she's liable to kill you.
[MERCENARIES yelling]
How'd Keum-ji find so many men?
I'm willing to bet that
he hired mercenaries
from all over the kingdom.
[gasps]
[MERCENARY K groans]
Where are you? We're ready.
Send up the signal.
Crap. We're totally outnumbered!
They're not showin'
signs of letting up.
He never had this
many men in the past.
[MAYA]
Jeaha!
You ladies decide
to take a time out?
We were just...
doin' a quick recon!
You ever notice
how he flies away
any time he doesn't
have a good come-back?
I'm pretty sure flying
away is his come-back.
Funny. I'm not even mad.
[BOTH yelling]
[OFFICER D] Guess the pirates
finally decided to attack.
It should be over
pretty quickly, though,
since we've got all
of those mercenaries.
Those idiots don't
stand a chance. Huh?
How did you get out?
You'd better get back
down below or else!
[OFFICER D]
Hold it!
What an idiot.
That's a dead end.
Give up now!
[BOTH yelp, grunt]
[YUN]
Aw, that looks painful.
Let me help. You'll feel better.
[ship creaks]
[yelps]
[BOTH gasp]
[OFFICER C grunts]
Oh, no!
Stay back!
Yuri!
Keum-ji wouldn't like it if
you damaged his merchandise.
So, why don't you let her go
and we can have a chat.
We could help each other.
I refuse to negotiate
with damaged cargo.
I'm gonna kill you to teach
the people of Awa a lesson.
No one disobeys Keum-ji.
[YONA]
Let her go!
She had nothing to do with this!
[YUN]
We're trapped.
And I've got the signal flare.
I could break free,
rush up on deck, and fire it.
No, that won't work.
I can't leave Yona and Yuri
to the mercy of these monsters.
They'd kill them both for sure.
Think, Yun, think!
I've gotta get these
guys outta the way
and get us up onto the deck.
Come on. Come on. Come on!
[YUN]
There was a time
when I would've just
broke free and run,
not caring enough to
save anyone but myself.
I could escape right now
if I didn't care about Yona,
Yuri, and the others, but I do.
[YUN]
Ik-su,
I think you would be proud
of the man I've become.
[YUN] I'm part of
something bigger now.
[ALL gasp]
[YUN] Something much
bigger than just myself.
[YUN]
I'm the one that you want.
As you can see, I'm not
what you thought.
I forced these two to help me.
You should just let them go.
That's a guy?!
I'm an undercover spy
for the pirates.
I was sent to
infiltrate this ship
to give away your
exact location.
The pirates sent you?
[OFFICER D]
You little brat!
You've just made the biggest
mistake of your life!
And I'm gonna make
sure it's your last!
--I'll beat you to death!
--[YONA] Stop it!
[YUN]
Hold on, please.
Listen to me for a second.
There's a bomb.
It's hidden on
this ship somewhere.
I'm the only one who
knows how to disarm it.
How do I know you're
not messin' with me?
Well, I could be,
but are you sure you're
willing to take the chance?
[OFFICER C]
Don't be stupid.
You really think we'd
fall for that crap?
I've got nothing to lose.
Believe me or don't,
it's your life at stake.
[YUN]
I've gotta get out on deck.
If I can send up the signal,
Sinha's bound to see it.
It's our only chance
of being saved.
Whaddaya think?
Dammit!
Take the girls back down below
and tie them up tight.
I'll take him up on deck.
And then we'll find the bomb.
[OFFICER D]
But...
[OFFICER C] Doesn't matter
whether there's a bomb or not.
I'm gonna cut off this
kid's pretty little head
and send it back to
his dirty pirate friends.
Get up!
[YONA]
Yun!
Hey! Stay back!
[yelping]
[gasps]
[OFFICER C]
All right. Let's go.
Just what in the hell
do you think you're doing?
Ah! Dammit!
[YONA yelps, grunts]
Don't you da--
[OFFICER C]
Where's the bomb? Well?
I knew it, you were
just bluffing!
I told you.
It's somewhere near the bow.
At least, that's what they said.
Let me up and I'll show you.
[YUN]
If I set off the firework here,
I'm not sure that Sinha
will be able to see it.
I've gotta get out
in the open to light it.
[OFFICER C] I had a feelin'
you were lyin' to us.
Guess I'll make an example out
of you after all, pretty boy.
Say your prayers.
[OFFICERS gasping]
Yona.
Step away from him right now.
If you don't do what
I say, you're dead.
Oh look, guys. It's the
feisty little redhead.
You think that bow and arrow
are enough to shake us?
[YUN]
Yona!
Come and get the firework!
Set it off! Use the lantern!
[OFFICERS]
Huh?
Ah?!
[YONA]
Hey, Yun. You have it?
I've got it hidden
inside of my dress.
[OFFICER C]
Hey! Stop her!
[YONA]
I hope this works!
[YUN]
I hope he sees it!
I did it!
[YONA]
Father,
I've become much stronger.
Am I making you proud,
wherever you are?
Next time on Yona of the Dawn,
Episode 22:
"History is Made at Night."