[HAK]
Well, crap.
I was hoping there'd be
something a little smaller.
Uh, hey there, Master Hak.
May I ask what you're doing
here in the middle of the night?
Sorry, Shop-keep.
I didn't mean to wake you.
If you came
during business hours,
you wouldn't have
to break down the door.
[HAK] I need a bow
and a small sword.
[STOREKEEPER 5A] Are you going
on a hunting expedition?
Yeah, sure.
Something like that.
I think it may turn out
to be a pretty long trip.
[HAK] Sorry about the door.
Whoa, you mean you're
actually paying today?
This much money'll take care of
your whole tab, and then some.
Thanks for all of
your help, Shop-keep.
See you again one day.
Lightning Beast...
What have you gotten
yourself into now?
Whatever it is, good luck.
[MAN 5A] Heang-Dea's back!
And he brought the
medicine with him!
Tea-Yeon,
how are you feeling?
I can't believe you got
there and back so quickly.
Told you I'd save the day!
Are you in any pain?
Can we get you anything?
Thanks for asking,
but I think I'm all better.
[ALL] Cute!
[ALL fawning over Tea-Yeon]
This is no time
to die, Heang-Dea.
All right.
I'm gonna head outta here and
check on the injured merchants.
I'll take this corpse with me
so you're not tripping over him.
Be a little more
careful, would ya?
[WOMAN 4C] Watch out,
blankets comin' through!
Oh, I didn't
see you there, Lina!
Sorry, madam.
Oh, my, you don't
have to be so formal
in the way you address me.
I'm glad I ran into you.
You can help me carry this load.
We need all
the help we can get
to tend to those wounded
by the Fire Clan's attacks.
Follow me and we'll see if we
can't ease some of their pain.
[gasps]
[YONA] These are the
merchants who were attacked
by members of the Fire Clan.
[WOMAN 5A sobbing]
Why did this happen to us?
We didn't do anything that
would provoke such violence.
You have to remember
that there's still hope.
The clan will take care of you.
You're not going
to be left alone.
[HEANG-DEA] Oops!
Oh, sorry.
I'm still a little
wobbly on my feet.
Uh... Did you hear me, Lina?
[YONA] I can't believe the
Fire Clan would hurt them
just to make sure
Su-won takes the throne.
There are so many
innocent people in pain.
[YONA] Su-won, are these
really your orders?
How far will you go?
Hey, don't look so sad!
Master Hak and the Elder will
make sure everything's okay.
Sure, they're hardheaded,
but they take great
care of their family!
Family?
Yup!
We consider everyone in
the Wind Clan to be family.
That means you're
one of us, too,
even though you're
still kinda new here.
[HEANG-DEA] Huh?
Aw, you made Lina cry.
That's not good!
No!
I didn't mean to,
Master Hak's gonna kill me.
[YONA] Hak, Mun-deok, the kind
people of the Wind Clan.
They must be filled with rage.
But they keep their feelings
hidden behind their smiles.
[YONA] What a strong
and proud Wind it is
that cares for me here.
Miss Lina.
What's the matter?
[YONA] I can't let them get
mixed up in my problems.
Not again.
[YONA] Hak!
[YONA] Tea-Yeon?
[TEA-YEON] Lina.
Hi there.
Who was that?
[TEA-YEON sniffles]
No one.
What's going on with you today?
I actually came to thank you.
[TEA-YEON] For what?
[YONA] For giving me
a warm meal to eat.
For wiping away my tears.
For cheering me up.
I'm so grateful.
Thank you for giving me hope.
I thought you'd be here longer,
but it sounds like
you're saying goodbye.
But I--
I wish you'd stay!
[YONA] There were nights
I thought I wanted to die.
But you were always smiling.
Even when your
little body was in pain,
you were still
so incredibly brave.
Watching you gave me courage.
[YONA] Tea-Yeon. I promise.
I won't forget you
or your people.
I'll carry your
strength with me.
Goodbye for now.
[TEA-YEON] I'm sorry, big
brother, but I've failed you.
I know that I promised
I would watch over Lina
and protect her.
But I don't think
I can keep her here.
[HAK] Looks like you're
doin' a better job
of guarding the gate today.
It's kinda hard to
get a nap in
if I don't have a
friend here to lean upon.
[HAK chuckles]
Lazy bum.
[TEU] Where are you
off to, General?
Out. I'm leaving for good.
Oh yeah?
Have a safe trip.
Hang on!
I'm a free man now.
Technically that makes you
the Wind Clan's next leader.
That job sounds
like a huge pain!
Wait a sec.
You're gonna leave
Miss Lina behind?
She doesn't know.
And I'm not really sure
how to say goodbye.
Please take care
of her for me.
A princess with
half a kingdom after her
is a pretty big burden to leave.
[HAK]
You knew this whole time?
[TEU snoring]
[YONA] Hak!
I've decided! I'm leaving!
You have to come with me.
[HAK] What's this now?
I have to go away.
If I were to stay here,
I'd be putting Fuga and
the Wind Clan in great danger.
[HAK] Don't worry.
The Elder knows everything.
It'll be fine.
You can live here peacefully.
No one from the outside
world will ever know.
You're setting out on your own,
but that's against my wishes.
You made me a promise.
You said you'd guard me.
That you'd help me survive.
I've renounced
my former status.
That means I'm
no longer a general,
or a servant to a princess.
You're interrupting my
first steps as a hired sword.
I'm no longer
responsible for your safety.
And as long
as you stay quiet,
Su-won won't bother
with you either.
[HAK] Step aside.
My mind's made up!
Doesn't make a difference.
I'm gone and you're staying put.
Do you have any money?
If we leave together,
then I'll have to protect you.
How would you repay me
for making sure
that you don't get in trouble?
A man with my skills can fetch
a high price for his services.
I'm afraid you don't have
the coin to afford me.
Unless you're planning
to pay me with your body.
I don't have
anything to give you.
And you know that.
Well, then that settles it.
You're staying.
Goodbye, Princess Yona.
Listen!
I want you with me, Hak!
[YONA]
Stay by my side forever!
But princess...
What are you saying?
You're so spoiled, used to
getting everything you want.
Aw, crap.
This situation is
really annoying.
[HAK] I'm gonna regret this.
All right, I give up.
You win.
[MUN-DEOK] You bastard!
--[HAK] Grandpa!
--What a disrespectful brat!
Were you here
the whole time?
[MUN-DEOK] I should
put an arrow through you
for every insult you said
to this brave, determined girl.
Thanks, Mun-deok.
[MUN-DEOK]
With you leaving, I feel like
I'm losing another grandchild.
[YONA] I understand.
Others said that, too.
That I'm their family.
It was nice.
And it's why I have to go.
I'll be fine.
Just promise me you'll
protect the Wind Clan.
Don't forget that if you ever
find yourself in trouble,
if your heart despairs,
or you need shelter of any kind,
we'll always
be here to help you.
We'll take your side,
no matter who your enemy is,
or what it means for our future.
All you have to do is ask,
and we'll be there.
[HEUKCHI]
Master Gang Tea-jun.
Leave me alone, Heukchi.
I'm busy sulking.
Pardon?
Father won't stop yelling at me.
He's pissed I acted on my own.
Well I have news that
might make you feel better.
What?
[HEUKCHI] We've received word
that Princess Yona
was seen around
the Wind Clan capital.
Fuga?
One of our soldiers
has confirmed
seeing a red-haired girl.
General Hak was
also seen with her.
The two of them
appeared to be headed
towards the
Northern forest on foot.
The Northern Forest? Why?
There's nothing
around there but trees.
We're not sure.
[GANG TEA-JUN] The princess
and the Lightning Beast.
Gah! This is my chance.
Call the troops to arms!
Those two fugitives are mine!
[YONA] Do you see anything?
[HAK] Nope. So typical.
Sending us out to find some ally
without even telling us
where he lives.
[HAK] The oracle?
[MUN-DEOK] Yes.
It's said that there's an oracle
who has foretold the future
of the Kohka Kingdom
since ancient times,
living somewhere in
the land of the Wind.
[MUN-DEOK]
Princess, if you're unsure
of what you
should do next,
I suggest you seek out this
oracle and ask him for advice.
Surely he will show you
the correct path.
[HAK] I've heard that in
the past the oracle lived
in the temple
at the royal palace
and was heavily
involved in politics.
However, Prince Yuhon
disapproved of his foresight,
and the oracle left the castle
for a more secluded existence
far away from others.
"Far away from others," huh?
Maybe we're close.
That definitely
describes this place.
[HAK] This area
may look uninhabitable,
but you could make a home here
if you put your mind to it.
Well, not you.
You'd probably fall off
a cliff the first night.
[YONA]
Although I'm Kohka's princess,
the Crimson Dragon Castle is
the only place in the kingdom
I'm familiar with.
I hardly know anything about
this land and its people.
Of course I'm unsure of
the path I should be following.
Right now I'm busy
just trying to survive.
I'm afraid we're
gonna have to camp.
That's the only way
we're going to be able
to search this place
thoroughly and find this guy.
Are you okay with that?
Yeah, of course.
I've actually kinda
gotten used to it.
[HAK] Unlike the mountains
behind the castle,
it gets chilly up here.
That's fine, I can
always just cuddle up to you
while you sleep.
[HAK] Man...
Fine by me.
But I might misbehave.
What do you mean?
If I'm overcome with passion.
Then I might
do something like this.
Stop it, Hak!
What do you think you're doing?
[HAK] Quiet. Footsteps.
It's forty.
No... More like fifty.
Enemies?
[HAK] There are too many people
for them to be scouts.
If these guys are after us,
they definitely mean business.
The king's troops.
Or maybe...
[HAK] Y'know, princess.
If you really were going to
cuddle up to me in the dark,
I'd want you to
be a little curvier.
Otherwise it'd be no fun for me.
[YONA] And just what
is that supposed to mean?
All right, then.
[HAK] Now that I'm
all warmed up,
it's time to kick some ass.
Stick close to me, Princess.
This could get messy.
[MALE SOLDIER 5A] He really
does move like lightning.
[YONA] I remember you
talking about him.
No one's faster with
a sword or spear than Hak.
If we ever fought for real,
there's no doubt he would
wipe the floor with me.
[YONA] Even at a dangerous
time like this,
my thoughts go
straight to you, Su-won.
[FIRE CLAN SOLDIERS] Attack!
Oh, come on!
Is that all you've got?
[GANG TEA-JUN]
You're quick, Lightning Beast.
[HAK]
Figures this is your doing.
[GANG TEA-JUN] I have been
waiting for this moment
for a long time.
Greetings, General Son Hak.
And of course, Princess Yona.
You remember me.
Now that I have your attention--
[HAK] Look, Princess.
The view from here is
breathtaking, isn't it?
What?!
I've been rehearsing
this speech all afternoon.
How can you just
ignore me like that?
Were you talking?
All I heard was a droning noise.
I'm actually not a general
or a "Son" in title anymore, so.
Sorry to ruin your big moment.
Oh, that's okay,
I can sub in your
nickname or something.
Wait...
What? You're not
a general anymore?
'Fraid not.
I'm just a traveler wandering
around looking for work.
So that means my actions
are mine and mine alone.
From here on out,
the Wind Clan has nothing
to do with any of this.
That's all well and good.
But I'm not here to
lash out against the Wind Clan.
All I want is the
red-haired princess.
And I'll take down
anyone who tries
to keep me
from getting her!
Don't give him
a chance to recover!
[SOLDIERS yelling]
Stop him!
Form a barrier!
Release the arrows!
You've gained
some weight, princess.
'Cause you made me!
[SOLDIERS yelling]
[HAK] This way!
For the kingdom!
[YONA] I'm so afraid...
There are arrows and troops
coming at us
from all directions.
It's too much
for even Hak to handle.
[YONA yells]
Aim for the Princess!
Hak! No!
Talk to me!
Are you all right?
You're hit!
Why are you suddenly
so concerned about my body?
It's unlike you.
Not funny!
Amazing...
Don't be impressed.
He'll be losing blood now.
Get him!
[MALE SOLDIER 5D]
We still can't find them.
[MALE SOLDIER 5B]
Look over there.
[MALE SOLDIER 5E] Will do!
[HAK] Do not move
from this spot, okay?
But Hak...
Your shoulder's bleeding.
That's not my blood.
Don't lie to
make me feel better!
Hak!
[HAK] If we leave together,
then I'll have to protect you.
How would you repay me
for making sure
that you don't get in trouble?
[YONA] He's still
trying to protect me.
[GANG TEA-JUN]
Where's the princess?
Don't tell me
she just disappeared!
[YONA] Gang Tea-jun.
[MALE SOLDIER 5A] Hak may be
serving as a distraction.
[GANG TEA-JUN] Find her
no matter what the cost.
[GANG TEA-JUN] He's starting
to look fatigued.
It seems that even the
lightning beast is human.
[MALE SOLDIER 5A]
It was a poison-tipped arrow
that hit him.
[GANG TEA-JUN] What?
You shot at the
princess with that?
We were certain that Hak
would put his own body
in harm's way if we
aimed our shots at her.
The poison
would've knocked out
any normal person by now.
He's stronger than we thought.
[GANG TEA-JUN] The next time
he turns his back to us,
hit him with another one.
[YONA]
Hak is going to be killed!
[HAK] Do not move
from this spot, okay?
[YONA] I should stay.
Even if I try to help, I might
end up making things worse.
[YONA] He'll be all right.
Hak's the strongest
person that I know.
He'll dodge it.
The arrow won't come
anywhere close to him.
I'll wait here quietly.
Just like he told me to.
Hak...
There's no way
he's going to die.
[YONA] No!
I didn't leave Fuga
to cower in hiding.
I must be brave!
I can't rely on Hak
to protect me forever.
[YONA] I refuse to be
a burden to those
who want to help me any longer.
I won't let Hak
sacrifice himself for me.
[MUN-DEOK] If you're unsure
of what to do next,
I suggest you seek out this
oracle and ask for advice.
[YONA] I don't need an oracle.
I know exactly what
I need to do right now.
[SOLDIER yelling]
[GANG TEA-JUN] Princess Yona?
[GANG TEA-JUN] Those eyes...
[GANG TEA-JUN] I never expected
that you'd come after me.
As a representative
of the Fire Clan,
I'm only here to talk to you.
Please, let's
calm down a little.
There is no need
for you to be alarmed.
I'm here to bring you back
to the Crimson Dragon Castle.
[YONA] To bring me back?
That's right.
His Highness Su-won will ascend
the throne tomorrow morning.
[GANG TEA-JUN]
My condolences for your loss.
It must have been
painful to lose your father
and then be chased
out of the castle.
If you come with me and tell
the truth about what happened,
you can stop Su-won
from becoming king
and get the vengeance
for your father deserves.
Doesn't that sound like
what you want?
Why aren't you hiding?!
[GANG TEA-JUN] So, Princess.
If you'll just come with--
[YONA]
If you're so well informed,
then why did the Fire Clan
put pressure on the Wind Clan?
Oh, no, you see,
those were my father's orders.
I had nothing to do with that.
And why did you
attack the merchants?
There are more important
things to be done.
But instead, you harmed
innocent people,
and then you ordered
your troops to kill Hak.
You don't care
about this kingdom at all!
[GANG TEA-JUN] Her eyes
are incinerating me.
Such rage.
I can't look away!
As for me, there's still
much I have to learn.
But I do know that I shouldn't
waste my time talking to you,
an unprincipled fool!
Princess!
[GANG TEA-JUN] I thought
I'd find that the princess
was a young, helpless girl.
But her crimson hair is a flame
that might burn me to ashes.
[YONA] Next time,
on Yona of the Dawn,
Episode 6:
"The Crimson Hair."