[IK-SU] If you don't mind,
I have a favor to ask of you.
When you leave, will
you take Yun with you?
[YONA]
Oh, wow!
[giggling]
Did you make this
all by yourself, Yun?
Uh, yeah. I had extra fabric.
Mind you, it's not silk or
anything fancy like that.
But whatever, it's not
like it's a big deal.
It's so unusual. I adore it!
I guess that's a good thing?
Hey, you have anything
to cut with around here?
[YONA gasps]
[YUN]
Hm?
My hair needs a trim.
[YUN]
Don't use that!
Oh, man. What a pain.
Princesses are so
high maintenance.
You really can
do anything, huh?
Only 'cause I live with
that pain of an oracle.
I had to learn about medicine
because he's so accident prone.
I am a great cook.
But, that came as naturally
as my extremely good looks.
No one asked about that.
You know... I like you.
[YUN]
Heh?
You take good care of Ik-su.
And now here you are
giving me a haircut,
even though you said
you hated royalty.
Well, Just so you
know, it ain't free.
The haircut, the medicine,
plus your room and board.
[YONA]
Oh, uh...
Mun-deok would be happy to pay!
Mun-deok, who? Y'mean the
Wind Clan's great war hero?
I didn't know
that he was a hero.
You dummy! The man
is a living legend.
He was as decorated as Yuhon
but more admired
throughout the kingdom!
Wow, seriously?
That's not the Mun-deok I know.
He's always been like
a sweet old grandpa to me.
A "grandpa"?
'Kay, you're all done.
Thanks a lot!
I'm convinced there's
nothing you can't do!
Well, I am a
genius, you know.
If I read a book once,
I can memorize it.
No way.
[YUN]
But, I've only read a few books.
I don't have access to more.
I know there are tons
of them out there
I could be reading right now.
It's frustrating.
You wanna find them?
[YUN]
Of course I do.
Listen, Yun.
But, it's no big deal, really.
I can always collect
more one at a time.
I guess for now, though,
this will tide me over.
Oh, what book is that?
Ik-su saw somebody
throw it away,
so he went and fished it
out of the garbage for me.
--[IK-SU screaming]
--[YUN] Then, like he does,
he tripped over
nothing and tore it.
He's alarmingly clumsy!
He's a major klutz!
I know the silly god talk
makes him sound weird,
but I know him better
than anybody else.
He's the type who
just can't... lie.
Okay, so, if you're gonna
head off on a journey,
you should pro'lly get going.
I mean, I'm way too busy
to keep taking care of you.
[chuckles]
[YONA]
Ik-su.
Uh. Princess.
That dress is quite beautiful.
Especially so on you!
[YONA giggles]
Yun made that for you?
That boy has so many
different talents!
He does.
So, did you ask him to go along
on your journey with you?
I gotta say. You remind
me a lot of Father.
What? I remind you of King Il?
Mh-hm.
No, I don't deserve such praise!
[YONA] You're clumsy, a cry
baby, and optimistic to a fault.
But still, I think you're sweet.
[YONA]
You know, Ik-su...
[IK-SU]
Yes?
[YONA]
In spite of his harsh tongue,
Yun really does
love you very much.
I couldn't bear the thought of
breaking up a family like yours.
I think it's better
for Yun to stay here.
I'm sorry, but I can't
comply with your request.
[YUN]
What request?
I can understand why you
want him to accompany us
on our journey...
if that's what he wants.
But, I just don't see how it's
even an option if he doesn't.
I understand.
I'm sorry. He really
should hear it from me.
[gasps]
[yelps, grunts]
[IK-SU]
Ow, that hurt.
[gasps]
[IK-SU]
Oh, hey Yun.
Your timing is perfect.
I was just talking--
[yelps]
Wanna tell me what
that was about?
Are you tryin' to get rid of me?
You want me to pack up
and go with them, huh?
Please, Yun. That's best.
I'll be okay.
The princess and Hak need
your help more than I do.
I'm not going with them,
and you can't force me to!
Listen, you're the kind of
person who should see the world.
You shouldn't be isolated.
But Ik-su...
[sighs]
And anyway, I can get along
without you, no problem!
[YUN grunts]
Ugh, I can't believe him!
What an inconsiderate jerk!
[whimpering]
Hey, Yun! Look what I found!
It's a medical book!
You shouldn't be isolated.
Caught some fish.
Lemme cook 'em.
How can you move around
that well already?
I heal really fast.
I have to stay alive.
Have to be invincible
to protect the princess.
Why do it? Seems stupid to put
your life on the line for her.
She couldn't do the same
if things were reversed.
What's in it for you?
Don't you make sacrifices
every day for someone you love?
You want to protect him,
and you take risks to
do that no matter what.
[YUN gasps]
You hungry? Here.
[YUN]
No, thank you.
Now what?
--[YUN grunts]
--[WOMAN yelps]
Someone help!
[YUN]
I'm so hungry.
All I ate yesterday
was a tree root.
There aren't even bugs in the
fields... much less any crops.
I'll have to steal food.
I have no choice.
The last time I tried this
I almost got myself killed.
I'll just have to be
smarter. Try harder.
It's me or them today.
[IK-SU yelps]
Here goes!
[YUN]
Money? Gold?
There's gotta be something!
[gasps]
[IK-SU]
I'm sorry.
I have nothing, child.
[screaming]
[YUN grunting]
--[YUN grunts]
--[IK-SU groans]
You... stay right there!
You're that kid...
with the rock.
[YUN] People in the
village are talking,
saying there's an
outsider walking around
with gold nuggets on 'im.
I know it's you! Cough it up!
[whimpering]
[IK-SU crying]
Wha? Hey, crying
isn't gonna save you!
I'm so sorry.
I gave away the last bit of gold
I had to another child earlier.
I'll find more and bring
you some, I promise.
I'll go and look for some
more right now, okay?
Then, you can have all of it,
and get yourself
something to eat!
[BOTH gasps]
I'm bleeding.
Well, it's your fault
for being such a dummy!
You should've known.
It's dog-eat-dog
around here these days!
Oh, it's all right, it doesn't
hurt. Don't worry about me.
Why would I be worried
about you, huh?
I'm threatening your life
with a hand scythe,
for crying out loud!
Okay, well, this was
a really great talk.
Are you freaking crazy?
[IK-SU chuckling]
[BOTH yelp]
Hey, we're not done here!
I wanna talk more about
those gold nuggets!
You're staying at
my place tonight!
Oh good, what a relief.
I was gonna have to camp
outside under a tree!
I'm Ik-su, what's
your name, little guy?
[YUN grumbles]
[YUN]
He's warm, so he's still alive.
I'll just put this on the wound.
[YUN]
It's so cold.
I'm starving to death.
Am I really gonna die like this?
[gasps]
A potato!
Yep, that's right,
and it's for you.
But, how did you
get it? From where?
It was a trade.
I haven't seen
one'a these in ages.
[YUN]
Hey, wait, why're you barefoot?
[grunts]
[YUN]
Where're your boots?
[IK-SU chuckles]
[IK-SU]
I traded them for the potato.
You gave them
away to get me food?
That was a dumb move,
it's freezing outside!
Why do something
like that for me?
What do you stand
to gain from it?
Nothing at all.
It's reciprocation for
the medicine you gave me.
You were awake during that?
Mm. And, it worked nicely.
I don't remember a time
my heart ever felt so warm.
As matter of fact, it's making
me cry just thinking about it.
[YUN]
Enough with the tears!
Man, you're a character.
Are all foreigners this
strange, or is it just you?
The world is full of
all kinds of people.
I don't visit the capital
much anymore, but when I did--
[YUN] The capital?
Oh, do you wanna go there?
Yeah!
I wanna get out of this town!
I wanna see everything
in the world!
Let's go to the capital
and the other empires!
I wanna go where I can
read books and study.
Wow! You know how to read?
Yup!
I'm so impressed!
I only read the easy
books right now.
But, I'm gonna read the
hard ones, too. Someday.
The next time I'm in town,
I'll bring you a book
from my travels.
I visit some very
interesting places.
Yeah? So what do
you do for work, huh?
Well... my job is
praying to the gods.
Are you serious?
[IK-SU]
Mm.
I let the gods lead me to
people who are in trouble.
I help restore
their will to go on.
I tell them how much
the gods love them
and I try to remind them
to love each other.
The gods don't exist.
There's no way they could.
[YUN] I don't think it's true,
but he doesn't seem like a liar.
Are you leaving to
go somewhere else?
You can't travel barefoot.
No worries, I'm gonna
make some sandals.
[YUN]
You can do that?
Someone taught me
a long time ago.
Wait! Can you teach me, too?
I can't believe it!
Yours look better
than the ones in the store,
and on your very first try!
Are you actually
gonna wear yours?
I feel sorry for the
straw that made them.
[YUN]
I learned a new skill!
Here, you take mine.
You mean it?
They're fine sandals.
In exchange... will you
teach me something else?
[chuckles]
[IK-SU yelps]
Hey! Are you all right?
Yeah, I'm just fine.
[YUN]
I had so much fun.
I haven't spoken that much
to anyone in forever.
I have a million more
questions I'd like to ask.
I really didn't want
him to leave yet,
but I couldn't say it.
Maybe the next time he shows up,
I'll be brave enough
to ask him to stay.
And then he'll be my friend.
I hope he wouldn't
think I'm a pain.
Even if he did, I don't care.
I just want him to come back.
[YUN]
This is all your fault.
I've always been alone,
but I didn't care before.
Now that you're gone, I'm so
desperately lonely all the time.
--[gravel crunches]
--[gasps]
[gasps]
[YUN]
Ik-su!
What in the world
happened to you?
Where're the rest
of your clothes?
I'm sorry, for not
coming back here sooner.
That doesn't matter.
I had collected so many gifts
in my travels to bring to you,
but the townspeople robbed me
because they thought
I would have more gold.
I lost everything I had.
They even took the books.
I think they were angry that
I didn't have any gold nuggets.
[IK-SU]
Yun, I have to go.
Far away from here.
Huh?
I love giving my life
to help people,
but it seems I only bring
out the worst in them.
Their desire for gold gets
in the way of my helping them.
[IK-SU] I wanted to
see you one last time.
Thank you for being kind to me.
I had such fun making sandals.
Goodbye, Yun.
[YUN]
I wanna go.
Take me with you.
I wouldn't mind, but I can't
go out in public much anymore.
Plus, I have to stay
out of the capital.
And, I have no books.
So? I don't care
about the capital.
And I don't need books.
I can learn from you!
Besides, you're clumsy. You
always fall and hurt yourself.
And I'm the only one who
can give you any medicine.
So, don't leave me alone!
I guess this is my chance, huh?
[YUN]
Hey, Ik-su!
Tell me the one about the
heroes in the old days!
You got hurt again?
Ugh, you're such a pain!
Hold on, I'll go
get the ointments.
I know you're right,
Ik-su, but still.
Who's gonna protect you?
There you are.
[YUN gasps]
Take these.
Your sandals were worn out,
so I made you some new ones.
All these years and
you're still so bad at it!
[IK-SU] Aw, c'mon,
I think my weavings gotten
a lot better than it used to be.
What about you?
[IK-SU]
Huh?
[YUN] Yours look even
worse than mine do.
[IK-SU]
Oh.
Just give me a second.
I'll be right back.
You're amazing.
Really, Yun. It's incredible.
All done.
Thank you.
[IK-SU chuckles]
[IK-SU]
They're perfect!
Hey! Check me out!
[IK-SU laughing]
[BOTH yelp]
[IK-SU]
I didn't fall down.
Ha. I didn't fall down!
I'm gonna be all
right on my own.
Ik-su, you know,
I called the princess ignorant
for not knowing certain things.
But all I have is book smarts.
I don't know anything
about the real world.
Man...
That's embarrassing,
don't you think?
Oh, Yun.
[YUN]
Listen, Ik-su.
You might not know this,
but your words have always
been absolute truth to me.
So at the end of the day,
if you tell me you want
me to go with them,
that's what I'm gonna do.
It might be my fate!
I mean, who am I to argue
with the gods about it?
It's not like you need me.
You even said yourself
that you would do just
fine all alone out here.
Our words have power.
They can manifest truth.
If you repeat things,
sometimes they become real.
So, I thought, if I kept telling
myself I'd be fine without you,
it would somehow
become the truth.
But no. It's not.
I'm not okay.
I'm so lonely. You haven't
even left, and I'm a wreck.
Don't be a pain! This isn't
gonna be good-bye forever.
[IK-SU crying]
So, have ya made a decision yet?
Yes. You're on board with
the idea, too, aren't you?
Long as he's not as much of a
burden as someone else I know.
And who would that be, exactly?
Oh, I dunno.
Okay. Sure you're all right?
Shouldn't I be the
one asking you that?
Hey, Yun, what's with
that giant bag you've got?
If it's books, leave 'em behind.
They're too heavy to carry.
I'm not bringing books.
Then, what are you
bringing? Lemme see it.
This bag here's
for the princess.
We can hide her in it if we see
Su-won's soldier's patrolling.
Don't know if I like that.
[IK-SU]
Hmph.
I've prepared for a few other
emergencies, too. Wanna see?
That's okay, we trust you.
We don't have all day.
Huh?
Thank you for having us.
Goodbye. I'll miss you, Ik-su.
I'll be praying for your
safety as you travel.
Hey, you're the one who
said you wanted to see
what I was bringing,
so don't leave me!
Have a safe trip.
[YUN] Come on, we need
to get a move on.
We got three giant
mountains to climb
before it gets dark tonight.
Okay.
Oh, so you think
you're in charge now?
Well, it would make
sense, wouldn't it?
I am qualified,
as a beautiful genius.
Whatever you say.
[YONA] I'm sorry, Father,
but in order to survive,
I must learn to take a life.
I must learn to kill.
Next time, on Yona of the Dawn,
Episode 9:
"Wavering Determination."