[YONA] After leaving the Blue
Dragon Warrior's village,
we traveled on for many days,
hardly ever stopping to rest.
[YONA]
Until finally...
[gasps]
[YONA]
It's a port town!
Hak, that's the ocean
down there, isn't it?
How pretty! I've never seen it!
I know this place.
It's Port Awa.
An Earth Clan territory.
[YUN]
So, you've been here before?
[HAK] Yeah, the old man brought
me here a long time ago.
Gija, you sense
the Green Dragon?
Yes, but...
His movements are so quick
that they're giving me vertigo.
--Are you okay?
--Well, that can't be good.
I guess tracking the
Green Dragon Warrior
must have sapped
most of his energy.
We've all had a
really long journey.
Before we go and
do anything else,
maybe we should rest and
find something to eat.
I can't wait to go and
check out the port!
Hold on!
None of you blend in
with a crowd at all.
Especially you in the mask!
I kinda remember my way around,
so I'll go get supplies.
The rest of you stay hidden.
But, Hak, I wanna go exploring.
Y'know, you've been lookin' a
little ragged lately, Princess.
[YONA screams]
How dare you
breathe such insults?
You are a vision of
l-l-loveliness, Princess.
[HAK]
You've got bags under your eyes.
Your hands are all scratched up.
Take it easy today, or you're
gonna wear yourself out.
I don't have any idea what
you're talking about, Hak.
[YONA]
He can see right through me.
It's so frustrating.
Make sure you're careful
while you're down there.
The last thing we need is
you getting into trouble.
[HAK] You guys stay outta
sight while I'm gone.
Oh. I'll leave this with you.
It stands out too much.
[yelps] Heavy!
And listen, White Snake.
There's no safer place for
the princess than with us.
[HAK]
If it comes down to it,
I'm hopin' the masked guy
with the little rat
knows how to fight.
[YONA]
Hey, wait a second.
Don't be gone for
too long, okay?
[HAK] It's been a while since
I was in a busy town like this.
I wish I had time ta look around
a bit longer but I need to--
[PROSTITUTE A]
Hey, hot stuff.
[HAK]
Uh.
How 'bout a good time?
Please, step away.
I've got a younger
woman waiting for me.
[HAK] Maybe it's just me, but
the longer I'm in this town,
the more it seems like everyone
here is a kinda depressed.
I guess it's none
of my business.
I gotta hurry up
and find some food.
--The others are waiting on me.
--[WOMAN] Please leave me alone!
Come on, now.
Be a good girl and show us
officers some affection.
We'll even be generous enough
to pay you for your time.
If the price is right, that is.
Please, let me go.
You're hurting me!
[HAK] Those officers are acting
like a coupla scumbags.
They should be
protectin' the people.
I wanna do something, but
the princess is my priority.
[WOMAN]
No! Get your hands off me!
Somebody! Help!
--[footsteps]
--[OFFICER B] Huh?
Well, now I've gone and done it.
These officers don't have any
idea how to woo a pretty lady.
Who the hell are you guys?
You think you can just
attack officers of Awa?!
Exactly how many people
do you plan to assault today?
You don't have any
respect for beauty.
[OFFICER C]
What's wrong?!
[OFFICER D]
What's going on here?!
[HAK]
Crap!
[STRANGER]
Oops.
--Hello, dear. Let's run.
--Who are you?
Stop them!
Back off.
[OFFICERS gasp]
[whistles]
You're in great shape.
Does that mean you're
a soldier or something?
Nope, I'm just travelin'
through town.
So you're a tourist, huh?
Guessing you've had more
than a little fight training
based on your moves.
What? You mean you
love the way I move?
[HAK]
Keep dreaming.
[OFFICER D]
Dammit, I don't see them.
Check over there!
[OFFICER E]
Right!
Well, it looks like we lost 'em.
[grunts]
Sorry, my dear. I'd love to
stay and get to know you,
but I'm afraid I've got to run.
Hold on.
This gentleman will see to it
that you get home safely.
Wait a second.
I don't have time
to drop every-- Uh.
He's gone.
That man. Who was he?
[GI-GANG]
Welcome home, Jeaha.
Ya made plenty-a noise while
jumpin' around out there.
And performed a perfect landing.
Right, Captain Gi-gang?
Ya showoff.
I'm bein' serious here.
You don't wanna go around
attractin' attention.
I know, I know, but
I was in a hurry.
[GI-GANG]
What happened?
Don't tell me the
officers were after ya.
[JEAHA]
Yes, but I sensed a presence
that was far more
dangerous than them.
I see.
Then what was it that
had ya in sucha hurry
to get back here to us?
[JEAHA]
Ancient powers.
The White and Blue Dragon
Warriors are here in Awa.
[YUN] You're telling me
you didn't buy any food?!
That was the whole reason
you went into town
in the first place!
Sorry. It's just that there
weren't any good shops open.
Well ,you're just a ton of help,
aren't you, Lightning Beast?
I guess we'll all have
to go to port tomorrow.
Uh! Yes! Awesome!
[HAK]
I'll let him cool down some
before I tell him
I punched an officer.
Sinha, are you
sensing him as well?
[SINHA]
Mh.
He's close.
[GIJA]
The Green Dragon Warrior
is somewhere out
there on the ocean.
[YUN] You guys felt the
Green Dragon's presence
over this way, right?
Hopefully, he's
still around here.
I'll meet up with you
guys in a little while.
I'm going back into town.
I wanna pick up
some weapons there.
Mr. White Snake, carry
this until I get back.
You're not my boss!
But, Hak.
[HAK] The officers
saw my face yesterday.
Everyone will be a lot
safer if I'm not around.
Hey, this time,
actually buy some stuff.
[HAK]
Will do.
[YUN] I think something's up
with the Lightning Beast.
He's supposed to
be guarding you,
but this is the second
day he's gone off
and left you alone with us.
Well, maybe he trusts that the
three of you will protect me.
Do you really think that
might be the reason?
[YUN] Could be he snuck
off to go see a girl.
Ah. I think we're getting
pretty close now.
[YUN]
Whoa, that's a pirate ship!
[YONA]
What?
It's definitely not like any
of the ships I saw in the port.
The dragon, could
he be a pirate?
[GIJA gasps]
Is everything okay?
His presence just...
Vanished.
[JEAHA]
Who do we have here?
Well, well, well.
So fate brings us
together once again.
You care to hang out for
a little while, friend?
No. I've got things to do.
You're not interested
in who's chasing me?
More officers?
Hmm. Well, in a
manner of speaking.
But don't worry about it.
I'll make sure to keep you safe.
Here? Really?
Isn't it a little early
in the day for this?
That's exactly why it makes
for a perfect hiding spot.
[HAK] I think this is
the kind of experience
you'd rather have
alone with the girls.
Oh no, mister,
please don't go yet!
So sexy!
Ohh. I can't believe
that handsome rogue
just stopped my heart with
a single smoldering look.
Hey! I need to see
how you did that!
I didn't do anything.
I'm used to gettin' this
from pretty girls.
My village back home
is full of 'em.
Really? Where're you from?
Please, tell me.
Sure. It's Fu-- Uh. Y'know.
That's a very interesting style
of clothing you have on.
Where are you from?
Uh. Well I, uh. I'm from--
[HAK, JEAHA chuckle]
I'm from, uh, from Awa.
I've lived here my entire life.
But these nice clothes
come from the Khai Empire.
Y'see, this is a port town,
so merchants stop
here all the time.
Really?
Then answer me this.
What's wrong with
the people here?
At first glance this
place looks normal,
but no one seems to have
any light behind their eyes.
You're a sharp man,
aren't you?
A powerful lord named Yang
Keum-ji controls the port of Awa
and therefore runs
the entire town.
All the citizens here
are afraid of him.
[HAK]
Is that so?
He also profits from some
illicit side businesses.
Illicit?
I'm afraid so.
In my opinion, taking a
person's freedom away
is the ugliest thing
you can do in this world.
Any man who forces someone
else to serve him is rotten,
and should be returned to
the earth from which he came.
Wouldn't you agree
with me, friend?
I serve someone as
a loyal bodyguard.
Uh! But that's terrible!
No, it's not.
Protecting her was my decision.
Uh...
[HAK] With all this talking,
I've said way too much.
[JEAHA] I don't get how
you can be a bodyguard.
Though, I do know three
bodies I'd love to guard
--for the rest of the night.
--[PROSTITUTES] Oh!
[HAK] You've got some
strong beliefs about freedom.
Sounds like you've
had some hard times.
Well, you see--
[YUN]
Hey!
What the hell do you
think you're doing?!
It's Yun.
And the princess.
This does not look good for me.
Now, before you get angry,
this isn't what it looks like.
This guy made me come here.
Where'd he go?!
I promise I was there
with someone else.
What're you doing
hanging out at a place like
this in broad daylight?
And what are you doing
in a place like this?
Gija said he could feel
the Green Dragon Warrior's
presence coming from this area.
We didn't know it'd
be this kinda place.
Or that you'd be living
it up here. Ya perv.
[HAK] Um. You got the
wrong idea, Princess.
[YONA]
Listen, Hak.
From now on, just tell me
when you wanna visit
a woman of the night.
I didn't realize you were
into that kinda thing.
I'm not.
Nice try, but now we all
know your smutty secret.
[growls]
[HAK]
What the hell?
Where did that
beauty-obsessed weirdo go?
[JEAHA]
Whew, that was a close one.
I let my guard down
for just a minute,
and the White Dragon Warrior
managed to sneak up on me.
And there was another
powerful aura, too.
Someone whose presence caused
my heart to drum faster.
[HAK] You've got some strong
beliefs about freedom.
Indeed I do.
[JEAHA]
The legendary Four Dragons?
A master I'm supposed to serve?
Not a chance.
Being born with a
destiny is slavery.
It means that you'll
never truly know freedom.
But I refuse to submit.
I'll change my fate.
Nobody can force me
into servitude.
Not even the
Crimson Dragon King.
[GIJA]
He did what?!
He's a liar.
Visiting an immoral place.
That scoundrel must
have no shame!
Yeah. He's lost my respect.
[HAK]
Now hold on.
I'm not the pervert you two
are making me out to be.
Come on, guys. Quit saying
all these bad things about Hak.
We should support him,
even if his interests are
immoral and degrading.
You're not exactly helpin' out
with my situation
here, Princess.
[HAK grunts]
[YONA yelps]
[HAK]
Don't make a sound.
[OFFICERS chatting]
[HAK]
It's those officers.
We should pick up what we need
and get the hell
out of this town.
[YUN]
That requires leaving the alley.
Are you able to get a read
on the Green Dragon Warrior?
I'm afraid not;
his aura has disappeared.
[WOMAN]
Excuse me.
The girl from yesterday.
That's me. I just wanted to
thank you for what you did.
No problem. Though you
shouldn't be out here
while those shady
officers are around.
I know it's kind of dangerous,
but I work nearby, so I have
to walk through these streets.
It's just not safe--
[grunts]
--[YUN, GIJA, YONA] Stare.
--Let's go talk elsewhere.
[WOMAN]
Huh?
[YUN] What? You beat up
an officer yesterday?
You could say that.
Another guy did
half the beating,
if that makes it any better.
Gee. What a courageous
duo you must have made.
And I'm guessing you caused
a huge scene. Am I right?
I really was trying
not stand out.
Sure.
I can't believe they assaulted
you out in the street.
Are they always so brazen?
Yes, they are.
They trash our stores,
and then demand bribes
so it doesn't happen again.
They take any girls they want.
The only thing we can do
is try and stay out of sight
and not provoke them.
[YONA]
Who's in charge?
That'd be Yang Keum-ji.
And who's that?
I heard he's the one who
calls all the shots in town.
And everyone's too afraid of
the consequences to cross him.
[WOMAN]
Yes, that's right.
He's even got the
officers on his payroll.
Everything is corrupt.
All the merchants
in town are forced
to pay him an incredibly high
tax just to do business.
Most can't afford it.
What's even worse are
the rumors going around.
We live in constant fear.
You poor people.
No wonder everyone
is in such low spirits.
And what makes you say that?
It looks like a
pretty lively town
from everything I've seen today.
You might think that
at first glance,
but it seems like everyone's
faking their smiles to me.
[HAK] She may have grown
up sheltered in a castle,
but she still notices
when people are upset.
And the pirates?
What pirates?
We found a boat anchored
in the cove nearby.
If there are thieves
or bandits around,
they're pro'lly adding
to the crime and corruption
already going on.
Actually. They're somewhat
protective of the townspeople,
and they've never harmed anyone.
Wait? Seriously?
[WOMAN] Sure, they've
commandeered a few ships,
but only certain ones.
Those owned by Yang Keum-ji.
Where's the cargo? We done?
Everything's been
loaded up already.
We just gotta hand all of
it off to the guys at port
and we're done.
Hey there, Lookout.
See anything suspicious?
[JEAHA]
Nope, all clear!
Excellent. Looks
like we lucked out
and won't have to deal with any
of those damned pirates tonight.
[JEAHA]
Excuse me!
Yeah? What is it,
something wrong?
[JEAHA] What "cargo" were
you talking about just now?
Huh? Are you stupid
or something?
You know we're here
to get the drugs
that were smuggled in
from the Khai Empire.
[JEAHA] What do you plan to do
with them once you've got 'em?
Turn this into a town
full of addicts.
Once the customers get hooked,
we'll be able to name
any price for the product.
[JEAHA]
Ha, ha. You're despicable.
[BOTH]
Uh?
Have you no sense
of beauty, Officer?
Wait, who is that?
What the--?
[JEAHA] Apologies for not
introducing myself sooner.
I'm your charming downfall.
My friends are here.
And right on time.
[OFFICER F]
Uh.
Pirates!
Move yer asses. Take that ship.
[PIRATES yelling]
[OFFICER G yelps]
[OFFICER F]
Fight back, men!
Lucky shot,
but I'm afraid that's the only
one you're going to get.
It's my turn!
[grunts]
[OFFICER E]
Whoa! Look, he's flying!
Aw, don't be scared.
This won't hurt much.
[OFFICER F] How dare you
filthy pirates get in our way?
[OFFICER F grunts]
Cowering in front of an officer?
That's not very
good form, is it?
Oh, c'mon.
Quit ragging on me why don'tcha
and watch your own back.
The only way to get
Captain Gi-gang's respect
is to stand up for yourself.
I can't help that I'm
not the best fighter.
I was just a fisherman
until five years ago.
And yet your work with a pole
leaves much to be desired.
Hey-yo, Captain Gi-gang!
I found the drugs.
They're below deck.
Then burn 'em up with
the ship, ya dumbass.
So, Keum-ji wasn't on board.
Where'dja put tha officers?
Oh right, we put
'em in a rowboat
and launched it into the ocean.
Ya didn't kill
any of 'em, didja?
'Course not!
But it's gettin' hard
not to, Captain.
They'd kill us all in a
heartbeat given the chance,
so why do we have
to pull our punches
and show those bastards mercy?
It'd be better for
everyone in town
if those corrupt officers
were gone for good.
As stupid as ya lugs are,
I can't help but love
each 'n every one-a-ya.
And I won't let
those I care about
carry the sin a murder
on their shoulders.
[ALL crying]
--[DOK] Mommy!
--[TATSU] Forgive our dumbness!
--[MAYA] I love you!
--[GI-GANG] Mommy?
[GI-GANG] I don't remember
givin' birth ta yer ugly butts.
Hm. What's wrong with you?
Yer bein' awful quiet.
It's nothing to worry about.
My right leg's just
been aching lately.
I bet ya kinda like it, huh?
Well, now that you mention it.
Do ya want me to
show you real pain?
You can't ask for permission
when you're already doing it.
[JEAHA] My leg has never
felt like this before.
The dragon's leg
that conquers the sky.
You say this power
you got is ancient,
but I'm amazed ev'ry
time that I see it.
Seriously, Jeaha. We all wish
we could move like you do.
It's always so cool to see
you flying across the sky.
It gets me super excited to
know that you've got my back
when I'm going into a fight.
[JEAHA] If only I were
"exciting" cute girls right now
instead a bunch of sweaty guys,
I'd be having a much more
enjoyable evening for sure.
[DOK]
What?
[DOK, MAYA, TATSU yelling]
Yer hidin' yer true feelings.
You'll have to forgive me
for keeping the others
at arm's length, Captain.
All that talk of brotherhood
makes me itchy.
I've gotten a little
too cozy here.
When I fled my village
13 years ago,
I never thought I'd have
another real home.
But then I found you
and the other pirates.
You welcomed me, and even
after seeing my ability,
no one ever looked at
me like I was a freak.
They're idiots.
And they're far too good to me.
Ha! Maybe you're just not as
special as you think you are.
You know, for a mother figure
you're not being very
encouraging right now!
Anyway, I plan on
sticking around,
at least for the time being.
That is, unless you've grown
tired of dealing with me.
I thought that those comrades'a
yers were comin' to recruit ya.
My comrades?
You mean the Dragon Warriors?
Don't make me laugh.
That's a relief ta hear.
Yer ability's a big help,
and I'm gonna need
the extra manpower.
Eventually, we're gonna
track down Keum-ji.
And it'll be a hell of a fight
trying ta take that bastard out.
[JEAHA] It's not like you to be
so uncertain about an outcome.
[GI-GANG]
I don't wanna watch
my little band a
dumbasses fall apart.
They've got good hearts.
I just wish there was some
handsome ones among 'em.
You have the most beautiful
young man in town
right in front of you, Captain.
But there is someone else
who could be more handsome!
Tell me everything about him.
He's a traveler who I
met him in town earlier.
I don't suppose this
mystery man can fight, can he?
Yeah! Only got a glimpse
at his technique,
but what I saw
was extraordinary.
That means he's probably
purty strong, huh?
Right!
He's strong, he's handsome,
and he's super manly.
He's just your type--
Go capture him immediately!
Aye, aye, my Captain!
[JEAHA] He'd be the perfect
fighting companion,
smoldering alongside
me on the battlefield.
Wait, didn't he mention
some nonsense
about serving as
a lowly bodyguard?
Not to worry!
I'm sure I'll win him over
with my impeccable charms.
There's no way he'll be
able to resist my beauty.
He's all mine!
[GIJA]
This way? No.
That way--? No. Where is he?
[JEAHA] If all you want
is to protect your master
because you were told from
the time you were born
that it was your destiny, then
you are a slave to your cause.
Next time on Yona of the Dawn,
Episode 18: "Bond."