[YONA] You mean to tell me
you're the oracle?
In that case, you must've known
I was coming here before I did.
Yeah.
[IK-SU] It's my job
to sit in contemplation
and listen to the
voices of the gods.
Then I bring their
message to the people.
They tell me all kinds
of things about our world.
[YUN] You seriously
call that a job?
It's not like you
get paid for it.
You just sit around
praying all day!
All right, give me
those filthy clothes.
Remember, all that crazy talk
about hearing the voices of gods
is what got you
kicked out of the castle.
[YONA] Is that really why
they kicked you out?
[YUN] Are you serious?
You're the kingdom's princess,
you should know these things.
[YUN] Outta the way!
I'm workin' here.
[YUN]
You're the kingdom's princess,
you should know these things.
[YONA] I was clueless
about things that went on
in my own home.
Hak! I'm with you!
Follow the sound of my voice!
[YONA] Hak!
Here, hold this.
[YUN] Move aside.
[YUN] His fever's high.
[YONA] Hak...
[YUN]
I gave him some medicine,
but his fever
won't break for a while.
Tonight will be the worst of it.
We'll have to watch him.
Please, you have to save him!
I'm trying my best.
You think I want him
to die on me?
Look, I'm not a trained
doctor or anything,
but you shouldn't be taking
my help for granted like this.
[gasps]
It's rude.
You haven't thanked me
once for helping you.
What about him?
Have you thought to thank him
for saving your life?
I bet it's not the first time
he's almost died to save you.
[IK-SU] Don't worry.
The gods have a plan for Hak,
death isn't coming
for him tonight.
He'll get better very soon.
[IK-SU] Yun, you should
speak to her more gently.
You know how
I feel about royalty.
They don't deserve our respect.
[IK-SU] Yes, but remember,
she's fighting a
difficult battle, too.
Why don't you and I
go for a nice walk outside?
Yun knows what he's doing
when it comes to his medicine.
He's saved me from certain
death more than once.
[IK-SU yells]
Are you okay?
[laughs awkwardly]
I'm curious.
Why do you live
all the way out here?
I followed
wherever the gods led me
and this is just where
I happened to end up.
But I suppose that
doesn't answer your question.
It's home.
It may be desolate,
but I can still see
the beauty in this place.
Hey, Yun?
Uh...
I want to thank you.
For helping us.
I'd like you to teach me.
About oracles
and everything you do.
I may seem clueless,
but I'm not stupid.
Please, I want
to learn all I can.
Well, you sound stupid.
Because I'm not an oracle.
I just take care of one
since he doesn't seem
capable of
doing it himself.
[YUN] I'll tell you, though.
The oracles used to possess
an authority that no one,
not even the king,
could challenge.
[YONA] Really?
Yup.
The people worshipped
and revered them
as servants of the gods.
The oracles were highly
influential in political matters
and even turned the
course of pivotal wars.
In fact, they once
did away with a king
because they said
he angered the gods.
They had so much power,
the royal family
began to feel threatened.
Under King Junam's rule,
the Kohka Kingdom gained
strength and influence
faster than it ever had before.
This renaissance
was due, in large part,
to Prince Yuhon's
military exploits.
He held the power and didn't
want to lose it to oracles,
who could hold
authority over him.
So my uncle
banished all the oracles
from the castle
to protect himself.
Don't you find it difficult
to live in the
middle of nowhere?
No, I don't.
I'm not fond of
people as a whole,
and Ik-su is more
comfortable out here.
[YUN] The capital cities have
been taken over by the rich.
Meanwhile, the villages
are poor and struggling.
Ik-su's generous to a fault.
He wouldn't stop trying
to save everyone.
All the poor.
When he couldn't,
he almost went crazy.
I don't know what
he'd do without me.
[YONA] Thank you.
I would like to
learn more from you.
[YONA gasps]
Where did Hak go?
[yelps, yells]
[YONA] Stupid Hak...
[YONA sobbing quietly]
Where are you?
[HAK] Ouch.
[HAK] Hope you haven't
been badmouthing me
like this the whole time.
If I had known this
is how I'd be rewarded,
then I never would've
saved you in the first place.
[HAK]
Why are you crying?
Did you have a
nightmare or somethin'?
Don't be silly,
I wouldn't cry over a dream.
Oh, really?
What are you doing out here?
[HAK] I was just trying
to find my glaive.
Why didn't you wake me up
to tell me that?
Oh, I see.
The princess doesn't
like sleeping all alone.
Want me to sleep with you?
I will.
[YONA] I can't believe you!
How could you be so stupid?
Geez, enough
with the name-calling.
You nearly killed
yourself trying to save me.
Please, Hak.
You have to be more careful.
You can't leave
without telling me.
I don't know what
I'd do without you.
I need you by my side!
[sniffling]
[HAK] You know...
I do kind of wanna die.
[YONA] What?
Even with that ugly face,
you still make me feel
tingly and weird inside.
It'd be worth it.
I'd gladly sacrifice my own life
to see how hard you'd cry.
[loud thump]
[BOTH groaning]
If you don't want to,
just dodge it.
Dodge what?
I thought you wanted
to check your temperature
so I pushed out my forehead.
Was I wrong?
Uh... No.
That's what it was.
This high fever's got
my brains all scrambled up.
Really? Because it feels
like your fever's gone.
Eheheh!
[HAK] Your hair...
[HAK] I'm sorry
about that, Princess.
I'm afraid it was all my fault.
No, it's okay.
I feel so much lighter.
I don't mind parting with it.
I hated my hair the way
it was, long and unruly.
[SU-WON]
I think your hair is amazing.
Breathtaking.
I kind of like it shorter.
What about you?
Looks good to me.
[HAK]
"I need you by my side."
She said it like it was nothing.
Well, like I said,
it's not your hair,
but your brain that's weird.
Better shut your mouth
or I'll shut it for you!
[BOTH chuckling]
[HAK] I'm sure you're still
holding on to that hairpin,
even though your hair's
too short for it now.
I guess some feelings never die.
[HAK]
Huh? The oracle lives here?
Seriously?
Yeah.
Wow. It's not what I expected.
I imagined it would
look a lot more like a shrine,
even out in the wilderness.
I mean, an oracle worships
all the time, right?
Come on!
Ask before you stuff your face!
[HAK] Oh, divine oracle,
thank you for the food.
[YUN]
I'm not an oracle, dumbass!
Speaking of, does anyone
know where Ik-su went?
[YONA] There you are, Oracle.
What's the matter?
[IK-SU sniffling]
[sniffles loudly]
[IK-SU]
I was just meditating.
I chose to focus on you.
This world and
how you fit into it.
The gods have a plan
for you, Princess Yona.
Do you want
to know the gods?
And hear them speak?
[YONA] I'm confused.
Mun-deok said I should
seek out the oracle
and have you
show me the way.
But is that best?
To allow you to
determine the way for me?
I'm not sure.
I always thought it was best to
stand still and not take action.
But then we were chased.
Hak and I came
so close to death.
My blood boiled in my veins.
I had to do something.
I couldn't be still.
I found my strength.
I can stand for once in my life.
I found my will to live.
I won't die.
I'll protect Hak.
We will survive to the end.
That's the only thing I want,
so I have nothing
to ask the gods.
They cannot tell me
how to do that.
[IK-SU] Not so.
Your life weighs
more than other humans'.
A fate like yours won't
allow you any peace.
The odds were against you,
yet you survived.
As a result, a storm is coming.
One that will turn
the kingdom upside down.
What do you mean by that?
[IK-SU] Let me show you.
If you truly want
to fulfill your destiny,
and you cannot cool
the fire in your blood,
then allow me to deliver
the message of the gods.
[IK-SU] Darkness falls on earth.
With dragons' blood,
they arise once again.
Following the ancient pledge,
the Four Dragons will gather
to protect the sovereign.
The sword and shield
will awaken.
And the Crimson Dragon
will finally return from dawn.
[IK-SU groans]
One needs
extreme spiritual fortitude
in order to deliver
the message of the gods.
Quit bein' lazy.
I thought this was your job!
I don't know anything about
dragons or gods or oracles.
So how do I know you're not
just trying to con us, huh?
He's not that bright.
In your prophecy, you spoke
of the "Crimson Dragon."
Do you mean the one
from the old legends?
You've heard the legend
of this kingdom's creation?
Yes.
It is said that
the Crimson Dragon God
took a human form and came down
from the heavens to rule.
He was our kingdom's
first sovereign.
He's known as the Crimson
Dragon King to this day.
Father used to tell me
the story all the time
when I was a little girl.
[IK-SU] That's right,
but not long after the Crimson
Dragon God became human,
[IL] he was forced to fight with
the people he loved and ruled.
Evil quickly seeped
into his subjects' hearts.
They forgot the gods
they once adored,
and the kingdom fell to ruin.
The people, in their
desperate hunger for power,
even seized the
Crimson Dragon King.
Seconds before the people
were set to murder their ruler,
the heavens opened and four
dragons descended to the earth.
[DRAGONS] Crimson Dragon,
we have come to save you.
Destroy these faithless humans,
for they have no love,
and return with us to heaven.
[IL] But the Crimson Dragon
refused their request.
No.
Even if the humans hate me,
even if they betray me,
I cannot stop my love for them.
They have taught me
what it is to truly feel.
[IL] The dragons loved their
crimson brother very much.
They respected his wish
but swore to watch over him.
In order to protect
the Crimson Dragon,
the others gave their blood
to four loyal human warriors,
thereby granting each man
one of their powers.
One was given sharp claws
that could cut through
any Earthly material.
And to another,
the sharpest eyes
that could see ahead for miles.
A third was given the power
to jump high into the heavens.
And the fourth obtained
a strong, invulnerable body.
[DRAGONS] From this day forward,
you shall act as our avatars.
We have granted you our power
so you may protect
the Crimson Dragon.
It is your duty to defend
him with your lives.
[IL] These warriors,
with the power of dragons,
led the clans of the kingdom
and protected their brother.
They restored order
to a land mired in chaos.
In time,
the Crimson Dragon King
grew weary of battle, and
retired to his eternal rest.
At long last, the Dragon
Warriors' work was complete.
They mourned the loss
of their master deeply
and cried over
his lifeless form.
They couldn't tell
if they grieved
because they loved the man,
or if it was the divine
blood in their veins
crying out for the
loss of their brother,
the beloved Crimson Dragon King.
[IL] After the king's death,
the Dragon Warriors
felt their powers
were too much
for humans to fathom,
so they left their respective
clans and disappeared,
never to be heard from again.
The people who remained behind
formed the five clans of
the Kohka Kingdom we know today.
[YONA]
That's the story I was told.
But I don't understand
what it has to do with me.
Princess Yona, you told me
you wanted to survive, right?
[YONA] Yes.
Well, as you know,
you can't do that alone.
The moment you
come out of hiding,
they'll be after you again.
Hak is by your side,
and he'll protect you
as long as he lives.
Sadly, though, without
anyone but the two of you,
he will die.
Hey, wait a minute,
you can't just say
I'm gonna die.
I'm no oracle,
but I can predict this.
If--
[HAK groans]
Threaten us all you want,
we don't have any money.
Ha. Ha.
So as you can see,
your bodyguard's in bad shape.
You're going to
need formidable allies.
But who? What allies?
You're going to
have to seek them out.
The Four Dragon Warriors.
No way, you've
got to be kidding me.
They exist?
Are you serious?
They're real?
[HAK] Give me a break.
They're just ridiculous legends.
[IK-SU] No, they exist.
Even after all
of these centuries,
they live in the kingdom
with the Dragons' blood
in their veins.
They will be the allies
you need in order to survive.
[YONA] Oracle, I would do
anything to keep Hak from dying.
But are you sure
they'll assist me with this?
It's my problem
and it has absolutely
nothing to do with them.
The night you left the palace...
It was a miracle
you made it out alive.
You were supposed to
die along with your father.
Then you and Hak
miraculously survived the fall
from that cliff.
I call these
twists of fate miracles,
but I believe
it was your destiny
that kept you alive
and guided you here to us.
If you seek them out
and enlist their help
to travel as your allies,
it's not your problem,
it's the gods' will,
and they are entwined in it.
[YONA] The gods' will...
[IK-SU] That being said...
Heaven will only
show you the path.
You must walk it.
You must choose it for yourself.
[YONA] I don't know
anything about the kingdom.
All those years in
the castle... I was blind.
[SU-WON] There is no
helping your father now, Yona.
[YONA] I know nothing.
[SU-WON]
I think your hair is amazing.
Breathtaking.
[YONA] I want to know. I do.
All the things I was
blissfully unaware of.
People's true intentions.
[YONA] I want to become strong.
[HAK] Princess.
[YONA] Who said you
could get out of bed?!
[HAK] Oof!
I'm all healed up now.
I'm not going to die.
You hear me?
Hak, I want to do it.
I want to find the
Four Dragon Warriors.
[HAK] Yeah, and do what?
They might not exist, and if
they do, and we find them?
What if they don't
want to come with us?
[YONA] We'll cross that
bridge when we come to it.
If we stay here much longer,
we won't be able to leave.
I'll do anything
to keep moving forward.
I want to gain
strength to survive.
I want you to teach me archery
and hand-to-hand combat,
and to use swords.
I refuse to die
without getting justice.
And I can't bear the
thought of losing you.
I'll take any help.
I'll use the gods' power.
I'll choose their path.
Look, I said I'm not
gonna die, all right?
Well, if that's what
the princess really wants,
I guess we'll roll the
dice on this destiny thing.
Hak, you're being
so nice lately.
You're a good boy.
Um...
Would you mind not getting
so close to me right now?
Why not?
Because your breath is awful.
Why, you!
Hey! You've got a few wrinkles.
No, I do not!
[HAK] Careful,
if you keep making that face,
you're gonna look like a prune
by the time you're twenty.
[YONA]
Watch what I do to your face!
Let's see how you like this!
Quit whining, ya big baby!
Have you come
to a decision yet?
Yes.
[IK-SU] If you don't mind,
I have a favor to ask.
[YUN sighs]
'Kay, I think that's
gonna work just fine!
[YUN] Listen, Ik-su.
You might not know this,
but your words have always
been absolute truth to me.
Next time,
on Yona of the Dawn,
episode 8, "The Chosen Door."