[DOK]
Jeaha, you leavin' again?
You've been spendin' all
your time in town lately.
Hm. This time's different.
I'm recruiting.
[gasps]
[HAK] I've been getting weird
chills since yesterday.
Are you feeling all right?
I'm fine.
[groans]
Let's try goin' this way.
[YONA]
Mh-hm.
Poor Sinha must be miserable
waiting all alone for us.
We need to find the Green
Dragon Warrior quickly.
[YUN] He did look pretty
pathetic when we left.
[YUN chuckles]
Gija, do you feel anything?
I sense he's in this town,
but he moves around so fast.
Getting a bead
on him is difficult.
If only he'd hold
still for once.
[OFFICER A]
Get outta the way, now!
This'll teach you!
[WIFE]
Leave him alone!
--[WIFE] You'll kill him!
--[OFFICER B] You shut up!
No. How cruel.
All the officers seem to
do is terrorize this town.
[YONA gasps]
Stay here, Princess.
Leave it to me.
But I...
It'll be my pleasure.
No, you're way too conspicuous.
Let me handle this one.
Now, stand back--
Cool it, Lightning.
Don't strike yet.
You can't just bust in.
You look like circus freaks.
How rude!
Pirates sunk one
of Keum-ji's ships.
That's the word.
It happened yesterday.
The officers are more
on edge than usual,
so their brutality against
the townspeople is worse.
I understand how you feel,
but we must be discreet.
[OFFICER A]
That should teach 'em a lesson.
[OFFICER B] Yeah, I think
we've earned a drink.
All right.
Looks like the coast is clear.
Yeah.
Come on.
[HAK]
Hm?
Listen.
[GIJA, YONA, YUN]
Hm?
I've got something
I need to take care of.
Watch over the princess.
What? Wait, Lightning Beast!
Uh... What was that all about?
Look.
[GIJA, YUN]
Hm?
Uh!
[JEAHA laughing]
Talk about ugly!
Oh, this is rich!
He's not gonna be happy.
Well, this makes my job
of recruiting him
a whole lot easier, now
that he's a wanted man.
[HAK] Who've you got
your sights on now?
Well,
I'll admit I don't have any clue
what the guy's name is, but--
Where did you come from?
I dunno know where you
get off laughing like that.
'Cause you and I are in the same
sad predicament now, buddy.
We are?
[JEAHA laughing]
What an unfortunate
looking rapscallion.
Do you recognize him?
No, I'm afraid I've
never had the pleasure.
That's your ugly mug.
[JEAHA]
Ah.
[JEAHA] The artist who drew
these has gotta be blind.
[HAK]
Yeah, no kiddin'.
That's right! It's you!
[HAK]
Huh?
That poster almost made
me forget my mission.
I came here specifically
to find you.
Nu-uh. I'm not gonna
be your accomplice
in whore-mongering again.
Oh, no, no, no.
That's not why I'm here.
[HAK]
Hm?
You're the one that I want.
[BOTH gasp]
[VILLAGERS whispering]
Sorry, but I don't
swing that way, pal.
No, wait, that's not
what I meant!
This is all one big
misunderstanding!
I need a strong, handsome man,
so I've got a
proposition for you,
but we should probably go
somewhere more secluded
to talk about it.
The last thing I want is to
be "propositioned" by you
in a private place!
C'mon, hear me out--
Just back off!
[HAK]
Aw, crap.
I mighta hit him
a little too hard.
[JEAHA groaning]
[HAK gasps]
[HAK]
I think he liked it.
He looks way too happy for
someone with a nose-bleed.
This guy's a pervert!
[JEAHA]
You punch like a beast.
I like that about you.
[HAK] First brothels, now
all-out masochism? I'm out.
You won't get away that easily.
Uh.
There you are.
Princess, what
brings you here?
Gija said he sensed
the Green Dragon Warrior
in this direction.
Oh, really?
I feel something pulling
me over this way!
Uh. Wait!
What did you have
to do alone?
Oh, just a little
meeting with a pervert.
[YUN]
Heh?
What's a pervert?
Never mind. I hope you
never have to find out.
[HAK] It looks like I finally
shook him. I can't believe it.
For the first time ever,
another person freaked me out.
Ah well, good riddance
to bad rubbish.
[HAK]
Let's head this way.
[YONA]
All right.
Recruitment is turning out
to be a risky business.
[JEAHA]
White Dragon dodging
is not on my list
of favorite hobbies.
I've gotta come on even stronger
if I'm gonna get that
handsome lug to join my crew.
I'll assault him with my charm
until he simply can't refuse.
Once my prey's in sight...
I'll stop at nothing.
Uh?
[JEAHA]
I sense a presence.
[JEAHA grunts]
[JEAHA yelps]
[thud]
You'd think that since
I can fly I could avoid--
[JEAHA chuckles]
[HAK growls]
[YONA] Is this the guy who
helped you save that girl
from those officers?
Yeah, that's him.
but it's not like he and I are
friends or anything like that.
Can I meet him?
I would really prefer
that you didn't.
[HUSBAND, WIFE crying]
[ALL gasp]
It's coming from that same shop.
--Princess, wait!
--Yona!
[HUSBAND, WIFE crying]
[YONA gasps]
Excuse us.
We've done everything
they've asked.
Our little boy stood
up to the officers.
He took a hard blow...
and since then...
He hasn't moved at all.
[YONA] If I had only done
something to stop them.
[YONA]
Hak... these people...
...they're suffering,
and they need our help.
We have to do something.
[HAK sighs]
I'm sorry,
but I don't think there's
anything we can do for them.
I know that's true, Yun...
But still...
The way father ruled allowed
this evil to take root.
And now I see.
I bear the burden of correcting
his mistakes. I have to.
[YONA] How could people
be so unspeakably cruel
to one another?
[YONA] I have to make
this right somehow.
There must be a way.
[JEAHA]
Well, here I am.
So, this is what it means
to feel like an idiot.
When I was younger, I escaped
the Green Dragon's village
after living my life
as a prisoner.
I'm not the type to hide, but
I did, time and time again.
I found ways to
cloak my presence
so the other Dragon
Warriors wouldn't find me.
I thought, at last I had
found a safe haven.
I fooled myself into
believing I could run
for the rest of my life.
Who knew I would
ultimately be undone
by getting my big, fat butt
stuck in a stupid vase?!
I don't even care,
just help me out!
Nice to meet you, I guess.
So, what do you want
with me, White Dragon?
I should hate you
for catching me,
but you're a Dragon
Warrior, like me,
so you can't be all bad.
And you're almost
as attractive as I am,
which means I might
have to kill you.
Hm.
Look everybody, I trapped
the Green Dragon!
Hey! Don't lie,
I trapped myself!
It's like it was meant to be!
He fell right out of the sky,
practically into my hands!
You know that I'm a
wanted man, right?!
Parading me around like this
is a surefire way to get us
both thrown in the slammer!
[gasps]
[JEAHA yelling]
Wait a sec. Just how big is
that butt of yours, anyway?
You really think I've got enough
posterior to fill this thing?
I can't believe
I actually found you!
[JEAHA] Uh... Yeah, yeah,
do you have to gloat about it?
[GIJA]
Our destiny awaits us.
[JEAHA]
Hm?
You and I are bound together.
Our sole purpose in life
is to protect our master.
[JEAHA]
Protect him from what?
Wait a second.
Are you talking about the
king from that silly legend?
Not quite. It's kind
of complicated.
I'll explain it later.
Forget it.
[BOTH grunt]
[JEAHA] I'm extremely
fond of the lifestyle
I've created for
myself here in Awa.
I have no intention of
walking away from all of that
to join some stranger in
protecting an unknown master.
That's my final answer.
Hold on! You come back here!
You have a responsibility
as a Dragon Warrior!
The time's come to fulfill
our purpose in life!
Our forefathers
gave up everything
to pass their powers down to us.
Therefore, we can't let
their sacrifices be in vain.
We have the great honor
of realizing the dream they
cherished for generations.
Oh, gimme a break.
Do you really buy into all
the fairy-tale brainwashing
they shoved down your throat?
You've gotta have a mind of
your own somewhere in there.
Can't you think outside
the "Dragon Warrior" box?
If all you want is
to protect your master
because you were told from
the time you were born
that it was your destiny, then
you are a slave to your cause.
That's no life for me.
If that is the case,
then I pity you.
[JEAHA]
Huh?
There he is.
--Hey.
--Nope.
Sorry about earlier,
I know I made it awkward,
but I just wanted to talk
to you about something.
Sorry, pal,
but my grandfather
always warned me
not to talk to creapy strangers.
Well, I'm Jeaha.
That's my name. I'm a pirate.
There, now we're not
strangers anymore.
Now we can talk without
ignoring your grandpa's advice.
All right, spill it,
what do you want?
My captain is quite
interested in you.
I told her how strong you are.
No one's ever
impressed me so much.
We want you to come join
our ranks and fight with us.
Not gonna happen.
Aw, c'mon, just
meet her one time.
You can even bring
your master with you.
I don't see any harm in
a single meeting, do you?
It's outta the
question, y'hear me?
I don't think I've ever met
a man so devoted to his work.
Makes you even more attractive.
[YONA]
Sorry we took so long.
--[heartbeat]
--[JEAHA gasps]
Hello, I don't
believe we've met.
[JEAHA gasps]
[DRAGON] From this day forward
you shall act as our avatars.
We have granted you our power
so you may protect
the Crimson Dragon.
It is your duty to defend
him with your lives.
[JEAHA]
My leg feels like it's on fire.
It's as if my blood
is boiling in my veins.
What could this mean?
[HAK]
Hey, Is there somethin' wrong?
Are you feeling okay?
[JEAHA]
This young woman.
She's the leader of
the Four Dragon Warriors?
All this time, I've
been avoiding her?
You're running a fever.
[JEAHA]
Her hand feels so cool.
I know I should break free
and run away as far
and as fast as I can,
but something won't let me.
I'm rooted to this spot.
Some unseen force
compels me to stay.
Thank you for your
concern, young lady,
but I'm quite all right.
Green Dragon.
[gasps]
You're the Green Dragon Warrior.
Are you sure?
Well, no, but I've got
a feeling that he is.
Am I right?
[JEAHA] I have no idea
what you're talking about.
I'm just a traveler
making his way--
There he is! He's the
Green Dragon Warrior!
You're just a traveler, eh?
Okay, I give up. I'm him!
So, you're the one I've been
lookin' for all this time.
To think I've been
avoidin' you like the plague.
You're the man from
the other wanted poster.
Hak told me that you helped him
save a girl from those officers.
I'm happy to 'ave
finally found you.
[JEAHA] I guess the bond
between the Dragon Warriors
and their master is more
powerful than I imagined.
You can call me Yona.
What's your name?
[JEAHA]
Everything about this young lady
seems to be drawing
me in, mesmerizing me.
But that's just the
dragon's blood in my veins
forcing me to feel that way.
I mustn't mistake these thoughts
and feelings for my own.
My name's Jeaha. It's nice
to meet you, miss.
I've always dreaded this
moment, but here we are.
Does that mean you knew
I was coming to find you?
I've sensed the presence
of the White and Blue
Dragon Warriors around town,
but I had no idea they'd be led
by such a stunningly
beautiful young lady.
I've been writing and rehearsing
the lines I would tell them
if they ever brought
their master to meet me.
"I have no intention of
becoming your slave.
You are not my master.
Please leave."
[GIJA growls]
[YONA] I'm not their master, and
I don't force them to serve me.
The White and Blue Dragon
Warriors have agreed
to help me with something,
and I've sought you out to ask
for your assistance, as well.
I'm delighted such
a lovely young lady
wants me to help her out,
but I'm afraid that I can't.
You see, I'm not
like the others.
I won't live and die
by some silly legend.
This is my life, and I refuse
to give up my freedom.
I've never been one to
take life for granted.
I intend to live
mine to the fullest.
So, don't expect me to vow
to protect and serve you,
now or ever.
Jeaha.
There's no need to speak
to me so vehemently.
[gasps]
[YONA]
It's all right.
Guess I'll just have
to give up on you.
But, Princess!
I'm asking for his help,
not giving him an order.
I can't force him
to do anything.
I didn't think you'd
give up so easily.
It wouldn't be dignified
of me to push the issue
when you've been so clear
about your feelings,
but I'll admit I'm
really disappointed!
It's so strange. I find
it hard to pull away.
I'm just drawn to the
Dragon Warriors, I guess.
Well, it's disappointing
to me, too.
I haven't met such a beautiful
girl in a long while.
In any case,
I'm determined to recruit
this hunk to fight with me.
It's not dignified of
you to push the issue.
You mean Hak?
Yeah, this guy's
a filthy pirate.
He's been stalkin' me
and beggin' me to
meet with his captain.
Filthy minded, maybe.
You're a pirate?
We'll do it.
We'll meet with your captain
whenever you'd like us to.
[JEAHA]
Hmm...
Really? Are you
going to give us Hak?
[YONA]
Mh-hm. No, I'm not.
But I think we have a common
enemy, and if we join forces
we might have better odds
of taking him down.
[JEAHA ]
What exactly are you getting at?
[YONA] I witnessed Keum-ji's
officers kill an innocent child.
The memory of it
makes me tremble
with rage and sadness
even as I speak.
I'm furious, both with
the men who did it,
and with myself for
letting it happen.
I have to act.
I cannot bear to see
another child killed.
He must be stopped.
I can't say whether or not my
comrades will fight with you,
but if you promise
to bring Hak,
I can definitely
arrange something.
Okay, meet me at our
ship tomorrow morning.
[YUN] Why would you make an
impulsive decision like that
without discussing
it with us first?
I'm sorry, but I couldn't
help myself, Yun.
I felt compelled to arrange
a meeting with their captain.
What if they try to assault
us or take our stuff?
Look, the meeting was
solely my decision,
you don't have to come
if you're afraid.
Don't take me for a coward.
I'm going with you.
I will accompany you, as well.
Do you really buy into all
the fairy-tale brainwashing
they shoved down your throat?
[GIJA growls]
Sorry to put you in
an awkward situation.
Ah, It's all right.
But that guy better keep his
annoying face outta mine
if he knows what's good for him.
I'm surprised you're
so quick to give up
on enlisting him, though.
I can't make him do
anything he doesn't want to.
Wow, that's so
understanding of you.
I remember when I tried
to leave the Wind Clan.
You were completely unreasonable
about the whole thing.
I think you said,
"I don't recall ever
approving you to leave."
[growling]
[HAK]
Huh?
Hey, what's your problem?
Shut up, Hak, that's different
because you're special.
Special?
[chuckles]
Whaddya mean? What
makes me so special?
Would you forget
about it already?
Why do you have to go
and make things weird?
And as I recall, you
also said something
about being grateful I had
to stay by your side.
[YONA] You're so annoying
when you get like this!
Enough flirting, you two.
C'mon, dinner's ready.
Hi, my name's Yona.
Are you the captain
of this ship?
Yep, that's me.
Captain Gi-Gong.
So, Jeaha tells me
you wanna help us out.
That the reason why you graced
my ship with your presence?
Yes.
[DOK]
Wow, a girl!
[TATSU]
She's so pretty.
[RYEO]
Hey, wait a second.
[GI-GANG]
What's under the freaky mask?
[DOK]
Maybe it's another girl!
[TATSU] I'll bet that
one's even prettier!
Take it off!
[GI-GANG] Show us
your face or else, kid.
You shouldn't harass the man
with major trust issues!
Leave him alone!
I don't need some sissy onboard
who won't show his face.
I run a tight ship.
I got no room on this vessel
for people who I don't
trust with my life.
But you need manpower,
don't ya, Captain?
Give us a shot.
[GI-GANG]
I'll consider it if you can beat
every one a these dumbasses.
Don't you think that's
a little unfair to them,
considering how badly
they're outnumbered?
You're onto something.
The odds are stacked
against us, huh?
--Yep.
--[SINHA] Hm.
Thankfully, I could take
them all out by myself.
I'd like to see ya try!
[PIRATES yelling]
Oh good, a show.
[HAK]
So, how'd we do, Captain?
We knocked 'em all out.
Want us on your side now?
There's no use resisting, boss.
It's kinda like having three
more of me on the crew.
And their strength would make
us completely unstoppable.
Hm. You pass the test.
I'm so glad.
Yeah.
[GI-GANG] Now don't start
celebratin' yet, little missy.
What skills ya got
that I might need?
I don't believe in violence,
so I'm not going to fight.
But I can do just
about anything else.
I know how to cook,
to sew, and to hunt.
I can treat injuries.
I know how to make certain
explosives, and I'm gorgeous.
That ain't too bad.
So, what about you?
[YONA]
Uhh.
[GI-GANG] Why should
I let you join my crew?
I have skills, but they're not
as practical as the others'.
So, you're useless.
The last thing that I need is a
little girl gettin' in the way.
But, ma'am--
Think I should
let you help out
just 'cause you
hate Yong Kum-Ji?
We all want revenge, sweetheart,
but you gotta have a lot
more than your feelings
to sail with me and my boys.
Now, go back home
to your dollies.
She comes with us as
part of the package.
--We make no exceptions.
--Gija, it's all right.
[YONA] Captain Gi-gang
has a valid point.
That being said...
I will fight. I'll just
have to do it alone.
Uh.
[GI-GANG] This girl's
got a fire in her eyes.
Okay, then.
Let's see if you got what
it takes to run with us.
If you can prove to me that
your willin' to risk your life
for our cause, then
you can stay onboard.
[GI-GANG] But If you can't
cut it, your off my ship.
[YONA]
Come on, legs, a little farther.
One step at a time.
If I can just keep going,
and complete this task.
If I overcome my fear.
Next time on Yona of the Dawn,
Episode 19:
"Trial of the Cheonsu Plant."