[HAK]
Princess Yona.
We should really get going.
It's cold here. Isn't it?
We are on the
edge of the mountains.
[YONA]
In my time at the castle,
I never knew the cold
beyond its walls.
That life is gone now.
[YONA] I was born
in the Kohka Kingdom.
The Crimson Dragon
castle was my home.
My father, King Il,
had produced no male heir,
and had no queen
to bear him a prince
to ascend to the throne.
Our family consisted
of the king and me,
his only beloved,
fifteen-year-old daughter.
[IL] This year marks
the tenth anniversary
of the death of my father,
the great King Junam.
Our cherished land of Kohka
is a small kingdom
with powerful neighbors.
We have been plunged
into wars with them
countless times in the past.
Where's the princess?
I believe she's
still in her chambers,
prepping for the event, sir.
Oh, that's right.
Must be 'cause
he's coming today.
Huh?
What a child.
[IL] My daughter, Yona,
will soon turn sixteen.
For her sake and yours,
I pray that my ancestor,
the Crimson Dragon King,
will continue
to shower blessings
upon our beloved
nation forever!
[CROWD cheering]
[CROWD]
Long live King Il!
You look absolutely
stunning, Princess.
Please, forgive my rushing you,
but we should be there already.
Not yet!
This isn't right.
What did I do with that new
calico chintz I had on before?
[YONA]
Father! Did I miss it?
Yes, my dear.
The ceremony is over.
No way!
I'm sorry. I lost track.
[laughing]
No worries.
After all, it was merely
a formality, my dear.
It was not necessary for you
to make an appearance today.
Father, be honest with me.
Do you think my red
hair is weird-looking?
Huh? Of course
I don't think that!
You are the most beautiful girl
in the entire Kohka Empire!
Yeah!
I do think that's true.
I was blessed with a beautiful
face, if I do say so myself.
But my hair!
It's the worst.
It's just so bright red,
and it's impossible to control.
It won't behave!
And on today of all days!
Darling, your hair is gorgeous.
Hak. Tell her.
Your hair's lovely, Princess.
There's nothing weird about it.
In fact, everyone in
the kingdom admires it.
Your hair's perfectly normal.
It's your brain that's weird.
Silence, servant!
Father, punish this cretin!
He's not allowed to
talk to me like that!
Now, now.
The way you fight,
it's hard to believe
you're childhood friends.
And let's not forget that
Hak is one of the five generals
charged with
protecting our castle.
He's the Wind Clan's greatest--
I couldn't care less!
Why couldn't you find a
charming man to protect us?
You're one to talk, Princess.
If you ask me, you could
use some charm, too.
Huh?
You know, since your
boyfriend's visiting.
Su-won is here.
Ugh! Why didn't you
say something earlier?
Su-won?
Is that why she was
worried about her hair?
He's seen it her whole life,
why worry now?
[HAK] She's developed a
crush on him lately, I guess.
[MAID 1A] Princess, come back!
[YONA] My love! He's here!
[YONA] Sweet Su-won,
who's been by my side
since we were kids
and was always so kind.
My cousin, who's
three years older than me.
Today, after so long,
I get to...
[YONA]
...see him!
[SU-WON] I see you're just as
full of energy as ever, Yona.
May I ask why you're
in such a hurry?
Well, I heard
that you had arrived,
and I wanted to be
the first to welcome you.
Aw. What a good girl.
So will you be staying?
Hopefully longer
than last time you visited.
Of course I am.
My favorite cousin's sixteenth
birthday is a monumental event!
[sighs]
I can remember when you
were just a little toddler!
You're growing up
way too quickly!
Now, where are
your father and Hak?
I'd like to say hello.
See ya, little Yona!
[YONA]
He treats me like a child!
It's so annoying!
I'm almost sixteen!
I pulled out
all the stops for him
and he didn't even notice.
I'm wearing beautiful clothes
and put on the best makeup
that money can buy.
[HAK]
Talk about a waste of time.
You shut your mouth right now!
[YONA] Stupid Su-won.
[YOUNG SU-WON]
What's the matter, Yona?
[YOUNG YONA]
Leave me alone!
Everyone says you haven't been
eating anything at all lately.
Your dad is
worried sick about you.
Go away!
[YOUNG SU-WON]
It's all right.
This way no one
can see your face.
Okay? Now you can cry
without anyone knowing.
[YOUNG YONA]
I haven't been able to sleep.
My mom, she always used to hold
my hand until I drifted off.
I know.
We all feel sad,
but I'm sure her death
is hardest of all for you.
I've got an idea!
I can do all the things
your mom used to do for you!
Well, first of all,
you've gotta eat something.
You can have this pear
my teacher gave me.
Here you go!
I'll hold your hand until
you fall asleep, okay?
It'll be just like what
your mother used to do.
I'll wipe away your tears, too.
I'll do it so fast that no one
will notice you're crying.
Now, go to sleep
and wake up with a smile.
[YOUNG YONA] What a dummy.
My heart is pounding
so hard in my chest.
I'll never be able
to sleep like this.
[YONA] Ever since that day,
he's the only one
I've ever loved.
Hi! Good morning, Su-won!
I packed a delicious
picnic for us!
Let's go eat in the--
What's the matter, Yona?
If you're looking
for Lord Su-won,
he's at the targets
with General Hak.
It's so unfair!
Why does Su-won always
want to spend time with Hak
and never with me?
Now, now.
Those two haven't seen each
other in a long time, either.
Hyah!
[SU-WON]
That was pretty impressive.
Good job.
[HAK] Thanks, and I can
tell you've been practicing.
I'll hit a bull's-eye soon.
Just like you did.
I want to be an
archer just like them!
That is absolutely
out of the question!
I wasn't even comfortable
letting those two
handle weapons!
But you've never
even done it yourself!
No, and I don't ever intend to.
Ugh, you're such a coward!
What kind of king is
afraid to use weapons?
[SU-WON] Yona!
Come join us!.
I'll teach you
how to ride a horse!
Okay!
Su-won!
[SU-WON] Just stay relaxed.
We're not going to
let you fall off, okay?
[YONA] You sure?
I know it's a big,
scary horse,
but I'm getting
kinda crushed over here.
I'll crush your dumb face!
[SU-WON] It'll be all right.
You do like horses, don't you?
Yeah, I do.
[YONA] But I love you.
[gasps]
There's no need
for you to be scared,
I'll hold you tight.
[YONA]
His breath in my ear...
I've got chills.
[YONA] When we were kids,
he looked like a little girl.
He sure has changed.
Aren't we breaking
the rules riding like this?
Uh... I mean...
You seem like you
really understand
how to handle a woman.
I bet you have all the
ladies falling at your feet
everywhere you go, don't you?
[YONA] What are these words
that are coming out of my mouth?
So I'm right?
What?
No, not really,
not in the way that you mean.
But to be honest,
there has been some talk
of me getting engaged.
[YONA] Engaged?
[SU-WON] It's all right!
Nothing serious or definite.
Look, it's nothing you need
to concern yourself with.
You'll understand more
when you're a little bit older.
[YONA] Ugh, I'm not a baby!
Well...
I've been considering getting
married to someone, too.
To whom?
Hak, in fact!
[YONA] What am I thinking?
Inventing some imaginary
boy would've been better
than telling him
I'm marrying Hak!
He'll know I'm lying!
Well, what was I supposed to do?
I don't know any
other boys my age!
Wipe that stupid look
off your face, servant!
No, wait. I meant...
[SU-WON]
I think that's wonderful!
Congratulations to you both.
[YONA] He's so cruel!
I can't believe you, Su-won!.
How could you
ever buy that story?
I think you're
cruel for saying it.
What a pain in the ass.
[IL] I hate to admit it,
but you getting married
might not be too far off.
It's time we start
thinking in earnest
about finding you
a suitable husband.
[YONA] But... No!
I want Su-won to--
You can never marry Su-won!
No, Princess, don't!
My love life is
none of your concern,
so you can't tell me
who to love or marry!
--That's my business--
--[IL] Yona...
Ever since you were a baby,
I've given you everything
you've ever wanted
without a moment's hesitation.
Everything but weapons.
Beautiful jewelry and
ornaments for your hair.
A royal villa
and botanical gardens.
But no matter how badly
your heart may ache for him,
I simply cannot allow you
to marry Su-won.
You are the only princess
of our beloved kingdom.
That's not something
to be taken lightly.
Your husband will one day
become king of this great land.
[YONA] I don't understand.
He's the son of Uncle Yuhon,
your older brother.
Su-won is of royal blood.
[IL] Yes, that's true.
But as the king,
it's my duty to choose
a successor to the throne.
Why not him?
Su-won is brave
and compassionate.
He can handle weapons
and behave justly,
while you're nothing
but a coward.
I have my reasons
for appearing cowardly,
you know that well.
Since your mother
was killed by insurgents,
I can't stomach violence.
The royal family lives
under the constant threat
of harm and danger.
That's our lot.
It always has been
and always will be,
which is why I have
never remarried.
[IL] If you truly love Su-won,
let him be happy
and free from that burden.
[YONA] I don't understand.
I'm not sure that I ever will.
Does that mean
I have to marry someone
I wouldn't mind losing?
But that doesn't
seem fair to me.
Doesn't everyone deserve to be
with someone they truly love?
Oh, who am I kidding?
Even if I had father's approval,
Su-won would never
want to marry me.
I'll always be a child to him.
I guess that's it.
It's no use.
Su-won and I just
weren't meant to be.
[footsteps]
Hello? Who's there?
I know that it's you, Hak.
I'm not in the mood
for your stupid games.
[YONA] No! It can't be!
[IL] The royal family lives
under the constant threat
of harm and danger.
[panting]
[YONA] No! Help!
Someone! Please save me!
[muffled screaming]
Su-won!
[SU-WON] I'm right here.
[YONA] Su-won...
I'm really sorry.
I didn't intend to frighten you.
You burst in like
someone was after you.
What's wrong?
I-I was being
chased by a strange man.
[SU-WON]
There's no one out there.
[YONA] He was! I swear!
[YONA] He ran away...
That means he was after me.
A guard wouldn't have hidden.
[SU-WON] Yona!
[YONA]
Was he trying to capture me?
Because I'm the
king's only daughter?
[SU-WON] Calm down.
Please don't be afraid.
I'm going to keep you safe.
[YONA] Su-won.
I can't.
I shouldn't be in here
alone with you like this.
[SU-WON] Why not?
Because.
[YONA] If I'm in danger,
it puts your life at risk, too.
If you'd rather
Hak protect you,
I can help escort you
to his quarters.
I understand.
You're engaged, aren't you?
[YONA] That's not--
[SU-WON] There's no need
to pretend you're not.
If the two of you
are to be married,
then I suppose you
and I shouldn't be alone.
[YONA]
No. It was a lie. I love you.
I know you don't see me
that way, but you must know.
I love you!
Su-won, I love you! I do!
[YONA] I always have.
I always will.
The rain's eased up.
It seemed like
it would never stop.
[YONA] Did he hear what I said?
[SU-WON] I'll take you
back to your own room.
Better come along now.
[YONA] Wait... Su-won!
Listen to me!
Please, forgive me.
But you mustn't come any closer.
I may do something I'll regret.
Maybe I'm mistaken,
but when you told me
that you love me,
it sounded like
you meant romantically.
What if I said
you're not mistaken?
[YONA] If I do
love you romantically,
would you be upset?
[SU-WON] I'm overwhelmed.
I'm not sure what to tell you.
I've never seen you
as a woman before today.
Huh?
Then how have you seen me
all of these years?
Oh. Well, um...
I don't know, I guess I thought
of you like my little sister?
That's what I suspected!
Sorry.
[SU-WON] Forgive me.
I can be a bit obtuse.
Especially when it comes
to matters of the heart.
[YONA]
His face. It's turning red.
Did you lie?
About being engaged?
No, I didn't.
I never said I was
officially engaged.
Merely that it had come up.
What now?
Do you still think of me
as your little sister?
I'll only say this.
I can't hold your hand
until you fall asleep anymore.
It's not appropriate.
And besides, I would
probably be up all night.
[YONA chuckles]
That's fine with me.
Knowing you
think of me that way.
Not like a sister,
but as something more.
That's enough.
That's all I need.
Yona.
[YONA] Father.
I hope you can forgive me
but I can't help it.
I love Su-won with all my heart
and nothing can change that.
Though I don't yet understand
the ways of the kingdom,
I do know that being with him
brings me more happiness
than I've ever felt before.
[YONA] Five days later,
a banquet was held
at Crimson Dragon Castle
in celebration
of my sixteenth birthday.
[MEN] Happy sixteenth
birthday, Princess.
May it be full of blessings.
Thank you all.
My sweet little girl.
I can't believe she's
already turning sixteen!
Yes, I know!
[IL] Having fun, dear?
[YONA] Why yes, thank you.
But my hair is
extra unruly today.
It's my birthday,
it should obey me!
Always the hair.
Why do I even bother
talking to you anymore?
[YONA] Su-won!
Wait!
Your Majesty.
Care for a drink?
Just what I needed.
Thank you.
[YONA] Um... Was there
something you wanted?
[SU-WON] Let me see your hand.
[YONA] A hairpin.
Sorry for pulling
you away from your party.
I wanted to give it to you
in person, to see your reaction.
I hope you like it.
[YONA] It's beautiful, but--
With my unruly red mane,
I don't think I could
wear something like this.
Only someone with pretty
hair could pull it off.
What?
[SU-WON]
I think your hair is amazing.
Breathtaking.
Blazing crimson.
Just like the blush of dawn.
[YONA] Well, that was easy.
All it took was
one compliment from him
and suddenly I love my hair.
Hak?
The king has been looking
all over the castle for you.
So? Tell him I'm in
my room, resting for a bit.
Well...
I figured something was
going on between you two.
I'm sure you'll be
able to convince the king
to let you marry her, My Lord.
[SU-WON] Hak, it's not
like that, I swear.
Not at all.
And stop being
so formal with me.
It's weird when you act like
we haven't known each other
our whole lives.
Well, I know what
my place is in all of this.
Hey, listen.
Do you sense anything odd here?
I can't put my finger on it,
but something isn't right.
I feel an unwelcome presence,
like an intruder.
Yona mentioned
something to that effect
a few days ago, as well.
[HAK] She did?
You might want
to increase security.
There are a lot of
unfamiliar people here.
[HAK] Will do.
I'll put a few more men
on duty right now.
Stay with the princess,
would you Su-won?
[YONA]
He called my hair "amazing."
He said it was "breathtaking."
No matter how badly
your heart may ache for him,
I simply cannot allow you
to marry Su-won.
[YONA]
I have to convince Father.
I won't let Su-won slip away.
I could never
love anyone but him.
I think he loves me, too,
and would brave any danger.
The door's open...
That seems careless
without any guards around.
[YONA gasps]
Something's not right.
Why aren't there guards
stationed out here?
I didn't see any of them
on my way, either.
[YONA] Father, it's me.
[gasps]
No... No! Father!
[SU-WON] I'm sorry you had
to see that, Princess Yona.
[YONA] What happened, Su-won?
Please hurry!
My father needs help!
[SU-WON] There is no helping
your father now, Yona.
The king is dead,
and I killed him.
[HAK]
It's too quiet around here.
[MIN-SU] General Hak! Here!
I thought you might be
in need of refreshment.
Thanks!
You always know just
what I need, Min-su.
[MIN-SU] Why aren't you
with the princess?
I'm so used to seeing you by her
side as her protector, y'know?
Yeah, but it's awkward.
I'll let Su-won do the honors,
she's his problem now.
What?
She finally got the courage
to tell Lord Su-won
how she feels about him?
Not sure.
But it's only a
matter of time, really.
You know them so well,
it seems like you know
what they're gonna do
even before they do.
Well, we go way back.
We grew up together.
I wish them the best.
Yeah. They're so well-matched.
They'll have a long,
happy life together, I think.
[YONA gasps]
Prepare yourself, Princess.
Your death is crucial to the
health of the Kohka Kingdom.
[YONA] Su-won is the
only man I've ever loved.
All my life, I've only
had eyes for him.
Su-won!
How dare you commit
such a treasonous betrayal,
Lord Su-won.
[YONA] Su-won, my love.
How could you do this to me?
After all that we've shared,
am I nothing but a joke to you?
[YONA] Next time, on Yona of the
Dawn, Episode 2: "Broken Bond."