[YUN]
Lemme out!
You can't keep me tied
up in here forever!
I may be cute, but that
doesn't mean you get to keep me
in a cage like your little pet.
I've got some powerful friends.
And they're gonna be
super mad about this.
Lemme out now and you
can save your village.
Our Dragon Warrior will
protect us from any outsiders.
[YUN]
So this is the clan
who protects the Dragon
Warrior's bloodline.
How am I gonna get
out of this mess?
Maybe Hak and the princess
are gonna storm the place
and save me.
And, to your left,
you'll see a lovely view of
the White Dragon's home.
What the hell?
Why are the two of you getting
treated like tourists, huh?
Oh, hi, Yun. What's up?
What's up is my blood pressure!
[OLD MAN] I apologize for
the way we treated him.
You, get that boy out
of his restraints.
[MAN A]
But, sir...
We have a crimson-haired
guest with us.
Oh, my! Right away, sir!
What's going on?
I'm not sure. As soon
as they saw the princess,
everyone kinda backed off us.
It's weird. They're all obsessed
with her hair. But why?
[OLD MAN] Please forgive us
for acting so rudely earlier.
This village is where
the White Dragon,
one of the four
dragons of legend,
retired once his role in the
Mythical Era war was completed.
We've had to fight off many
power-hungry adventurers
who've shown up over the years
looking to obtain the
might of the dragon.
It's our joy to protect
the White Dragon Warrior,
and to ensure that his bloodline
is passed on to new generations.
This has understandably made
us wary of most outsiders.
[HAK] I understand
your predicament, but--
Is this ordinary?
--[WOMAN A] So pretty!
--[WOMAN B] Crimson hair!
[WOMAN C]
Wow! It's so beautiful!
[gasps] Hak, that woman just
called my hair beautiful!
I heard her.
Her hair color is pretty rare.
But is that really any reason
for everyone to
freak out like this?
Given our history, crimson hair
holds a very special meaning
for the people of this village.
The first White Dragon
Warrior served a master
who had hair that
burned like fire.
It's funny.
I always wished it
was a different color.
[OLD MAN] You should
feel honored to have it.
When we found you, you mentioned
that it was an oracle
who guided you to
this secluded village.
You could be the one.
The ancient king's heir who
we've been hoping would
arrive for thousands of years.
[OLD MAN]
Then again, maybe not.
[YUN, YONA, HAK groan]
So, now that we know
where the village is,
what happens if
she's not the one?
[OLD MAN] Anyway, the birdsong
is lovely this time of year.
[YUN] You can't just
avoid the question!
Hey, you're gonna keep me
safe, too, aren't you?
You know, if anything
strange starts to go down?
Dunno. I'll think about it.
If you don't mind my asking,
what makes your White
Dragon Warrior so special?
I mean, from the looks
of it, your entire clan
is direct descendants
of the original one.
Yes, that's true.
We may all be descended
of the same bloodline,
but only one person a generation
possesses the White
Dragon's power.
[OLD MAN]
That person is born
with the dragon's might
sealed in his right hand.
[WHITE DRAGON]
I wonder...
Why do mornings always
make my hand ache?
We have an emergency! The White
Dragon is in terrible pain!
[WHITE DRAGON]
I'm fine!
There's no reason to make
a big deal out of this!
[sighs]
Y'know, you're going to stop
this old woman's heart
one of these days.
I was afraid that you'd somehow
injured your sacred hand.
[WHITE DRAGON] You're always
overreacting to everything.
Besides, I'm not even sure
how I could hurt myself.
I live hidden away under the
entire village's protection.
It's backwards.
Shouldn't I be the one who
protects everyone else?
What would we do if you did?
Watching over you gives us
purpose and a sense of duty.
You were blessed with a strength
that can't be squandered
on day-to-day affairs.
And you're not only powerful,
you're more beautiful
than all the other
White Dragon Warriors
I've raised
over the years.
[WHITE DRAGON sighs]
[WHITE DRAGON] That's great.
But it's so frustrating.
I have such might,
but, when will I be able to
use it to make a difference?
When the time comes to use your
power, you will recognize it.
If your mother and
father were still alive,
they'd remind you
to have patience.
The power may not even
be needed in your lifetime.
If that's the case,
you should consider yourself
lucky to live in peace.
You can rest easy knowing
that the next White Dragon,
or the one after him, or one
later still, will use the power
to protect his master on your
behalf as you watch from beyond.
[WHITE DRAGON]
The next White Dragon.
[GRANNY] All you need to do
is rest easy in the village
and try not to worry
yourself too much.
[WHITE DRAGON]
When will this master,
who I'm supposed to
protect, finally appear?
[WHITE DRAGON]
I want to meet him soon.
I want to have a
purpose in this life.
[GRANNY]
By the way, White Dragon.
Ahhh. Unless I've miscounted,
you've reached the ripe
old age of 20 this year.
[WHITE DRAGON]
Yes, that's right.
Well, then, you're
around the age
where you should've chosen
a wife or two already,
wouldn't you say?
[WHITE DRAGON]
One! One is plenty.
If that's true,
then pick one already!
Soon there won't be any
more women in the village
who meet your lofty standards!
[WHITE DRAGON] Please, hurry,
master. I'm ready to serve you.
[VILLAGERS chatter]
[WHITE DRAGON] What's with all
the commotion this morning?
[GRANNY]
That?
Some outsiders wandered
into the village earlier.
What? We should
eliminate them quickly.
[GRANNY] Actually, I hear
there's something special
about them.
Apparently, the villagers
--have really taken to them.
--[WHITE DRAGON growls]
This place is supposed
to be a secret!
I hear there's a really
pretty young lady with them.
[WHITE DRAGON]
Of course there is.
There's no one trickier or more
deadly than a female assassin.
I'll take care of her.
White Dragon, wait!
[WHITE DRAGON] I may not be
allowed to leave this village,
but I can use my
power to protect it.
[YONA sighs]
Hey, what's with the long face?
This kinda seems wrong.
The villagers said when
a child with the power
of the White Dragon
Warrior is born here,
then the previous
White Dragon Warrior
loses his power soon afterwards.
They've been protecting this
bloodline all these years,
waiting for the day
when the dragon's might
will be called upon once
again to save the world.
But I'm asking them to give me
their greatest treasure
for something personal.
Are you giving up?
[chuckles]
Hey, Hak. Let me borrow this.
I won't give up.
The dragon's coming with us.
Besides, we've come
all this way.
We can't just turn back now.
[WHITE DRAGON]
No need to be alarmed.
There they are.
The scoundrels. How dare they
send this village into a panic?
My claws will make
short work of them.
Give yourselves up!
[YONA, HAK gasp]
[YUN]
Huh?
[WHITE DRAGON]
She has... crimson hair!
[heartbeat]
[BOTH gasp]
[WHITE DRAGON]
What's happening? My hand!
It feels like my blood
is flowing backwards.
[DRAGON] From this day forward,
you shall act as our avatars.
We have granted you our power
so that you may protect
the Crimson Dragon.
It is your duty to defend
him with your lives.
[screaming]
[WHITE DRAGON]
Is it possible?
Could this young
girl be my master?
Is she the one I've yearned for?
[WHITE DRAGON groans]
[VILLAGERS chatter]
[GIJA'S FATHER] Gija, the
first White Dragon Warrior
was born in the Mythical Era to
protect the Crimson Dragon King.
One day the king will rise
again, and when he does,
it is your duty to protect
him with your life.
But father, when will he come?
When will I be able
to use my power?
You'll know when you see him.
Your blood will cry out,
recognizing its master.
For it is the blood
of the White Dragon.
[GIJA'S FATHER] A blinding light
will flash before your eyes.
That will be your signal, and
the beginning of your journey.
[VILLAGERS chatter]
[groaning]
You gonna be okay?
[OLD MAN]
Look! His hand!
I've never seen
anything like this!
[WHITE DRAGON]
Dear father,
and all of the White Dragons
who came before me,
the men who protected
this clan and bloodline,
thank you.
So, then, are you
the White Dragon?
I am. The Dragon's blood
flows through my veins.
It cried out when
I first saw you.
[WHITE DRAGON] I've been
waiting for you. My master.
Your master? What are
you talking about?
What an amazing day this
is for you, White Dragon.
Our king has finally appeared
after all this time
and he's a little girl!
[YONA] King?
Why do they keep referring
to the princess as a guy?
It's because of the legend.
The king had crimson
hair, like she does.
[WHITE DRAGON]
My ancient master.
[YONA gasps]
[WHITE DRAGON]
Please, tell me your name.
It's Yona.
Master... Yona.
[YONA] So he's the
White Dragon Warrior.
With his smooth white skin
and shimmering silver hair,
it's easy to tell he's
not a normal person.
You're a very pretty boy.
Uh. You are mistaken!
It is you, Master,
who is truly beautiful.
[YONA]
Such flattery!
I'm sorry to disappoint you,
but I'm neither your
king nor your master.
You see, I'm actually
just a fugitive.
I want your power to
protect me and my friends.
Y'know, you could've phrased
that in a much better way.
I'm on a journey to reunite the
four Dragon Warriors of legend.
I've come to ask you for your
help first. Will you join me?
I would be extremely honored.
No matter who you are
or what purpose you have,
I'm your Dragon
Warrior from now on.
I'll serve you in any way I can.
For my blood compels me to.
I am now your humble servant.
That settles it. I'll be
leaving the village at once.
Our master commands it.
[OLD MAN] Right!
What is this nonsense,
young man?
[OLD MAN screams]
This calls for a celebration!
Prepare a feast in honor of the
Crimson Dragon King's return!
Immediately.
We've waited a long time.
Seeing you is a gift.
I'm so grateful
I lived long enough
to see your crimson hair shine.
And those adorable
but fiercely smart eyes.
And your blushing skin that--
[YONA squeaks]
Doesn't really look like
it's been taken good care of.
[YONA, WHITE DRAGON sigh]
[YUN]
Man, this is kind of strange.
Ik-su was right
about this location.
But I figured it would take
a little more convincing
to get him to join us.
I wonder if he's disappointed
that I'm a princess
instead of his king.
Or, if he's surprised
you're a fugitive.
That's the truth, though.
I didn't want to lie to anyone.
Why do you have that weird grin
on your face, Lightning Beast?
It's kinda freaking me out.
I was just thinking.
It was kinda fun
watching the princess act
like a total badass earlier.
Are you making fun of me, Hak?
You'll never know!
[WHITE DRAGON] My right arm's
tingling. My body's still hot.
As soon as I saw her,
my blood began to burn.
And I could hear the voice
of the ancient dragon
speak directly to my soul.
[WHITE DRAGON] After thousands
of years of waiting,
the day our clan has
longed for is here.
I've known my purpose in this
world since I was a child,
and my time is now is at hand.
Mother and Father,
please, watch over me.
[knocking]
'Scuse me.
[WHITE DRAGON]
Huh? What rudeness!
You can't just barge inside
my castle without permission.
[HAK]
Oh, yeah, sorry 'bout that.
What are you doing here?
[HAK] I came to see if
you had any useful stuff
that could help us out.
But you don't.
[growling]
[WHITE DRAGON]
Take this.
[HAK] Whoa. Wow, you're really
generous, White Dragon.
You may consider this
money a parting gift.
[HAK] Wha--?
Thank you for your service,
but now you're relieved.
I will be protecting the
princess now. So, you can go.
Oh, the other two are back.
[YUN] Umm... Why do I feel like
something terrible has happened?
[YONA]
What's going on?
Princess, let's find another
White Dragon. This one's dumb.
[WHITE DRAGON]
How do you not realize
you are no longer
wanted or needed?
There's no way a
pampered jerk like you
is taking my job,
show some respect.
It's destiny!
Why have you employed such an
idiotic worm as your bodyguard?
How are you already fighting?
He wants to fire me.
He even tried to bribe me
to convince me to leave.
Well, that would
explain the bulge.
I've gained some weight.
It's my sacred duty to
serve and protect her.
If you're not a
dragon, then leave.
No way!
Hak's been my friend
since childhood.
Even after I was chased
from the castle
and everyone turned
against me, he kept me going.
He's important to me.
I command that he
stay by my side!
[HAK chuckling]
Well, well. Y'hear
that, White Dragon?
I'm important. I guess
you're stuck with me.
We're giving this back.
If that's how you
really feel, Princess.
Don't look so sad.
I need you, too.
At the rate we've been going,
Hak is going to die trying
to protect me on his own.
So, I want you
to look after Hak
and make sure that he doesn't
end up getting himself killed.
Ohhhh!
This all suddenly
makes perfect sense.
You need me to protect him
because he can't
take care of himself.
Count on me.
I'll keep you safe,
but also watch out for
this vulnerable beast.
[HAK growls]
You may think you're
tough, but I don't need
some dainty "white snake"
watching over me, got it?
White Snake, huh?
You dare call a sacred
Dragon Warrior such a name?
[YUN]
Let's leave 'em both.
[VILLAGERS chatter]
Over the years, I've
raised four generations
of White Dragon Warriors
in this village.
And now, the moment I've spent
an entire lifetime dreaming
about has finally arrived.
I know.
Dimwit, a joyous occasion
like this is no time for tears.
[OLD MAN]
I... can't help it!
[VILLAGER A]
Goodbye, White Dragon.
Everyone, I told you that
you didn't have to come
and see me off.
[VILLAGER B] I can't
believe you're going already.
[VILLAGER C] We thought
we'd have more time
to say our farewells.
I can't linger.
The master I'm destined
to serve has come for me.
I'm taking my rightful
place by her side.
She needs my strength,
the same power you protected,
and that the previous White
Dragon Warriors passed on to me.
You're so noble!
I will never forget the
kindness that you've shown me.
I'm grateful to you all.
We'll protect this village
while you're gone.
Please, come back
as soon as possible.
[WHITE DRAGON]
Good. I'm counting on you.
This village must remain safe.
That way if something
happens to me,
[VILLAGERS crying]
the bloodline will be protected
and a new White Dragon
Warrior will be born.
Why would you even
imagine such a tragedy?
Please, don't ever die!
You're the best White
Dragon we've ever had!
[WHITE DRAGON]
Whoa. Sorry.
[GRANNY]
White Dragon Warrior!
Granny.
[gasps]
You're not leaving without
a bag of my famous rice balls!
[WHITE DRAGON grunting]
[GRANNY] It might get
chilly along the way.
Here's a coat and a change
of clothes I made for you.
And a decade's
worth of medicine.
Also serums and creams to
maintain your good looks.
Fine! You talked me into it.
Take this girl with you, too.
Hold on! I can't
carry all of this!
[ALL groan]
[panting]
[WHITE DRAGON]
Granny.
I'll probably be gone
for a long time.
I've left it to my uncles
to look after the village.
Huh? No one asked me
my opinion on that.
It's my responsibility
as the village elder
to take care of things
while you're away.
I know that, but, I heard
that your eyesight has
gotten pretty bad.
I may not see too well,
but I've got the energy
of a young maiden.
You're definitely
the liveliest one here.
[GRANNY]
I hope it lasts.
[gasps]
[GRANNY]
What's tomorrow gonna be like?
I'll wake up, but
you won't be here
for me to drag you out of bed.
You're going to be
somewhere else.
The clan's long-awaited dream
is coming true at last.
But, now I wish it wasn't. I
want a few more years with you.
[WHITE DRAGON]
Granny. Please, don't cry.
[chuckles]
[WHITE DRAGON] You've watched
over me my whole life,
always there, day or night
making sure I was happy.
Especially after my
parents passed away.
You're important to me.
Even when I'm in faraway lands,
I'll be thinking of you,
and wishing for your happiness.
So, watch your health.
And, try to lead a life of
peace in your final years.
[GRANNY]
Watch your tongue!
How dare you talk to me
like I'm some old biddy
who's going to keel over!
--Ohh.
--[WHITE DRAGON gasps]
I've still got plenty of
years left in this body.
On that wonderful day when
you've fulfilled your duty
and return to us, I'll
be the one at the front
of the line to
welcome you back home.
I promise you that, my darling.
[GRANNY]
No matter how many years go by,
even if I go blind,
I'll still be able to see
the glorious light
that radiates from you.
Make us proud and then come
back. Promise me you will.
[YUN sniffing]
So, which way do
we go from here?
[YONA] Did Ik-su say anything
about where we should go next?
Not a word. We're on our
own path from here on out.
Yun, your eyes
are all red again.
Shut up!
[HAK chuckles]
What should we do now?
You want to find
the other Dragons?
That's right.
Then, you're in luck,
because I can sense those who've
inherited the ancient powers.
Seriously?
Yes.
I can't pinpoint them
exactly from this far away,
but the Four Dragon Warriors
are like my brothers.
Our blood calls
out to each other,
even after all these years.
I've wondered what the other
Dragon Warriors are like.
Ah. That'll be super handy!
Handy?
All right, let's start by
climbing down this mountain.
[YONA]
Oh, I meant to ask.
What's your real name?
The one you were born with.
[WHITE DRAGON grunts]
Everyone there was
calling you "White Dragon,"
but surely you had
another name once, right?
May I call you by
your real name?
[WHITE DRAGON]
I thought my true name had died
with my mother and father.
No one else ever cared
about anything but my title.
Gija. That's my real name.
Gija. I like that.
Hm.
[YUN]
Hurry up, guys!
If you don't move it, we're
gonna leave without you.
[GIJA] Don't just assume that
you can put your hands on me.
This power, it's been waiting
to protect its master
for thousands of years.
Next time, on Yona of the Dawn,
Episode 11:
"The Dragon's Claws."