[YUN]
Okay, let's see.
So, if Gija's directions
are accurate,
the Green Dragon Warrior
should be nearby.
[GIJA grunts]
[HAK]
But if we keep going this way,
we'll run right into the capital
and Crimson Dragon Castle.
Right.
Let's travel along
the mountains, then.
It'll take a little longer,
but it'll keep you safe.
Yeah.
Sinha! You see anyone?
Well, then. Let's get going.
Your distance vision
is a huge help.
We haven't run into
a single soul yet.
Yeah! You're proving to be
quite useful, Blue Dra-- Uh.
So, I hear the Princess
bestowed a name upon you.
Sinha.
That's quite an honor. You
should be extremely grateful.
Now listen. Long ago, in ancient
times, the Four Dragons...
[YONA] Looks like Gija's
taken Sinha under his wing.
They're going to
get along just fine.
Along the way, we came upon
a desolate town in ruins.
I'd never seen anything like it.
This village.
Looks like it's
been abandoned...
...by all the generals
and the king.
[gasps]
[YUN] There's no irrigation,
so all their crops have died.
And any able-bodied men
have probably been taken
to the capital to be made into
soldiers for Su-won's cause.
[YUN]
Disease is spreading so quickly
those who are too weak
to leave can do nothing
but lay down and die here.
How sad.
[YUN] I was born in a
village just like this.
The Fire Clan has
such vast land,
but it's mostly
infertile and dying.
Their leader,
General Gang Su-jin,
spends more money
on his military
than he does his people.
Wow, what an ass!
[VILLAGER coughing]
Are you all right--? Uh.
No, don't get too close to him,
or you could get sick, too.
But, Yun.
This medicine won't cure you,
but it will ease your pain.
[VILLAGER groans]
Here, have some fruit, too.
[YONA]
Drink.
[VILLAGER] Are you from
the capital? From Sy-ka?
No, we're just passing through.
[VILLAGER]
I see.
Well then, have you
been to Kuto recently?
I heard the old king died
and they've already
crowned the new one.
I hope he turns out better.
[HAK]
Uh...
Uh.
[VILLAGER] The last king,
Il, was the worst kind.
[YONA gasps]
[VILLAGER] He avoided
conflict at all costs,
and bowed to any foreign
power who challenged him.
He destroyed the unity
between the five clans,
and the kingdom fell into chaos.
He did nothing
for the powerless,
those who relied on him most.
But he was never our king, and
so his ruin is poetic justice.
I hope, for the sake
of the next generation,
that the new king is
different. Just and brave.
Maybe he can save this kingdom.
Thank you.
It's been years since
anyone has touched me.
Your kindness has
almost made me feel
like a human being again, miss.
[YONA]
You're welcome.
Please, take care
of yourself, sir.
I hate to stop, but I'm
afraid nature's calling.
I'll be right back, okay?
[YUN]
I just...
...I couldn't say anything.
To be honest, I feel the same
way about how King Il ruled.
But still, he's the only family
the princess has ever known, so.
It's likely that no
one in the kingdom
will grieve much over
King Il's passing.
And, I'm sure, history will
say he was ineffectual.
Unfortunately, in this case,
no one cares what
a daughter thinks.
It's true.
Peace is just a fantasy.
Absolute peace,
with no conflict.
War is humanity's nature.
That said,
the king was an idealist,
but he was never a fool.
He had a strong will and
he stood by his beliefs.
I never saw him as a coward,
and I still don't.
Because I saw the wounds he
tried to hide from the world.
And I would never pledge
my life in service
to a fool or a coward.
[HAK] I failed to protect him
at Crimson Dragon Castle,
and I'll regret it for
the rest of my life.
So, you pledged your
life to serve him,
not only because of your
friendship with the princess,
but out of respect for the king.
[HAK]
Yes, that's right.
Even if the kingdom forgets.
At least I know...
you'll remember me and father.
Thanks to you, we'll live on.
[HAK]
How could I ever forget?
She had everything.
Glamour and beauty. The most
fortunate girl in the kingdom.
And now, she's alone, with no
one to look after her but us.
All she has left is the memory
of the father she loved.
I can't take that from her,
and I won't do anything
to tarnish it.
[crying]
[AO cries]
[gasps]
[bow creaking]
[YONA]
Not bad, but I can do better.
I'm determined to get stronger.
I have to, if I want to
protect Hak and the others.
[YONA] I will do whatever
it takes to keep them safe.
[IL]
Yona.
[gasps]
[IL]
Fighting isn't the answer.
Nothing is solved by taking up
a weapon against another.
[crying]
[YONA]
Father.
So, this is Chishin.
The capital of the Earth Clan.
[CHEOL-RAN]
Master Geun-tea!
General, what is wrong with you?
Oh, shut up. What are you
yelling about now, Cheol-ran?
[CHEOL-RAN]
It's the middle of the day
and you're not even dressed yet.
Our clan leader shouldn't be
such a careless,
scruffy lay-about!
It doesn't matter what I wear,
I'm still gonna be me.
Besides, I'm not
hurting anyone, am I?
I mean, would ya take
a look at the Wind Clan?
They get to wear whatever
they damn well please.
That doesn't seem
very fair to me.
Well, their clan is full
of good-for-nothing
deadbeats, Master.
Geez. I wish it were
like the old days.
I've been bored out of
my mind this past year.
There's no foreign
commerce coming in,
and our resources are dwindling.
This sure isn't how I envisioned
the Earth Clan's future.
[CHEOL-RAN sighs]
Why can't it just be more like
it was back in King Junam's day?
Capital was full of people.
And I used to be such a
beast on the battlefield.
I would slay all of my enemies
like a... a God of War!
[CHEOL-RAN]
That's out of the question now.
[GEUN-TEA]
Uh.
King Il forbade all
combat, remember?
So, you couldn't fight
even if you wanted to.
[GEUN-TEA sighs]
Besides, you call
yourself a War God,
but I remember a match
where you were beaten
by some kid called
the Lightning Beast.
Now, he's what I'd
call a War God.
Aw, you always know
just what to say, Cheol.
Anytime I need a humility check,
you're there at the ready
with a snarky comment.
I'm sorry, sir. I promise
you I didn't mean it.
[CIVIL SERVANT A]
Master Geun-tea!
Oh, have you come to insult me
and tell me how
to live my life, too?
[CIVIL SERVANT A]
Um... No, sir.
You're not going to believe
this, but King Su-Won is here!
[BOTH]
Huh?
[GEUN-TEA]
Well, I'll be, it's really him.
[CHEOL-RAN]
Uh, yeah, I can see that.
Now, would you hurry
up and go get dressed?
Seriously, you're going
to embarrass yourself.
Look, even General Ju-do
from the Sky Clan is here!
[GEUN-TEA] What the hell is
His Majesty doing in Chishin?
And why'd he only
bring two soldiers?
[CHEOL-RAN]
How am I supposed to know?!
I haven't seen you
since my coronation.
General Geun-Tea, you and
your clan are faring well?
Yes, sir.
[GEUN-TEA]
"King" Su-Won.
How'd an 18-year-old ascend
to the throne so quickly?
Makes me wonder.
There were some
odd circumstances
surrounding King Il's death,
like the princess's sudden
disappearance with General Hak.
But he is the son of
my mentor, Master Yuhon,
whom I deeply respected.
General Geun-tea,
if you don't mind,
there's something that
I must ask of you.
Sir?
Bet he's got a super
special mission for you.
It's probably some
covert operation
My throat is so parched
from the long journey.
Do you think that
I could trouble you
for a hot cup of tea?
[BOTH]
Huh?
Wow. The aroma of this
blend is intoxicating.
My wife will be
happy to hear that,
it's from her prized tea garden.
I'm not a big fan of it myself,
I find the smell overpowering.
[SU-WON]
It's delightfully floral.
[GEUN-TEA] She only dabbles
in cultivating exotic teas,
so you'll have to forgive her
if it tastes a little odd.
[SU-WON]
It's merely a hobby?
Then I'm doubly impressed!
What do you think,
General Ju-do?
I've never claimed
to be a connoisseur
when it comes to
the realm of fine teas.
That being said,
I'm appalled that the general
would dare to offer the king
anything less than
his finest stock.
What?
I offered him my
wife's favorite blend.
You've always been so
uptight, you know that?
Maybe if you could ever
wipe that permanent scowl
off of your face,
you might find a lady
to help refine your
unsophisticated tastes.
How dare you?!
You wanna fight me?!
Cheol, get my sword so I can
teach this jerk a lesson!
No, I won't help you pick
a fight with our guest.
[SU-WON]
General Geun-tea.
Your... Highness?
The tea was excellent.
I would love to see your
wife's garden while I'm here.
--[GEUN-TEA sighs]
--[JU-DO] What?!
If you wanna be
treated like a king,
you've got to stop being
so damned easy-going.
Otherwise, nobody's
gonna respect you!
I guess I do need to
toughen up, I'm sorry.
This milksop is
Master Yuhon's son?
Ha! What a pathetic excuse
for a man, let alone a king.
I see nothing of his
father's dynamism in him.
In fact, I seriously doubt
that they have anything
in common at all.
Master Yuhon was the epitome
of an indomitable warrior.
He's the only person
I've ever deemed worthy
of being my master.
Is this man even capable
of leading the kingdom?
Chishin castle is very different
than what I expected.
I'll bet it is.
I only wish you didn't have to
see it in such a sad state.
We've wanted to start
renovations for a long time now.
Problem is we don't have
the funds to get them done.
Hm. Well, I've heard
a lot of rumors, sir.
People say the reason the
castle's in such bad shape
is that you trashed it--
[HUI-DAE]
Master Geun-tea!
Old man Hui-dae,
is there something wrong?
There's been a terrible
cave in at the Udo mine!
Not another one? Any injuries?
Yes, sir. Ten of our best men!
I swear that mine's
a death trap.
Have we exhausted it yet?
[CHEOL-RAN]
Excuse me, Your Majesty?
Yes? What is it?
May I ask why you made the
journey to Chishin in person?
Wouldn't it have been easier
to send someone else
on your behalf?
Let me guess,
you have some top-secret
business with General Geun-tea.
No, I'm just on a sightseeing
tour of the kingdom.
That's not nearly as cool.
Sorry!
[CHEOL-RAN]
No offense,
but if you wanna take
a leisurely vacation,
I wouldn't suggest hanging
around this crumbling kingdom.
In case you haven't
noticed, Your Majesty,
things have gotten
awfully bad here in Kouka.
The worst is Awa, though-- Uh!
Hold your tongue, Cheol.
Don't forget you're talking
to our king, dumbass.
I don't mind, really.
[GEUN-TEA]
Your Majesty.
Uh?
I'd like to pick
your brain a bit.
What'd you think of your
predecessor, the late King Il?
What're you doing, sir?
Not to be irreverent,
but I always had my doubts
about the way he chose to rule.
He shied away from conflict and
conceded much of our territory.
It weakened our nation, and
the citizens suffered for it.
"For the people," was his motto,
but he didn't rule that way.
He damaged our relationships
with the Shin and
the Sai in the south,
and we feared an all-out
attack from the Kai Empire.
If I had witnessed this
dangerous pattern of failure
and humiliation continue
for much longer,
it's possible I might've
been the one to rise up
in rebellion against him.
Ahh! Are you crazy?!
Geun-tea!
[GEUN-TEA] I was only saying
I might've taken action.
I'm not implying
that a rebellion actually
occurred or anything.
[JU-DO]
He has some nerve!
Shut your mouth! Pay him
no mind! Are you insane?!
Please, ignore him, sir,
the Earth Clan would never
dream of staging a rebellion.
[GEUN-TEA] What I really wanna
know is how will you rule
more effectively
than your predecessor?
Can we trust that
you'll be any better?
Sightseeing through your
kingdom while it crumbles.
Enjoying your tea while
the poor suffer and starve.
Are you doing everything within
your power to save this land?
At your coronation, you promised
you would restore this kingdom
to its former glory, and
bring it back to what it was
in the days of the ninth king.
Do you solemnly swear to uphold
the vow you made to your people?
Yes.
I'm willing to pinky
swear if need be.
[groans]
[GEUN-TEA]
This guy's got dirt for brains!
[SU-WON gasps]
[GEUN-TEA]
Huh?
[SU-WON]
This rock is simply fascinating.
It's a rock like any
other hunk of earth.
Can't you see
it's been enshrined?
Obviously, it's not just
any rock, it's special.
[GEUN-TEA] What a shame.
He's nothing like his father.
This fragile man-child
doesn't have what it takes
to restore this land
to its former glory.
Kouka Kingdom is doomed.
It's been enshrined
because we found it
deep within the Udo mine.
Oh, I see. And may I ask why?
[GEUN-TEA]
It's an old Earth Clan custom.
We enshrine objects
from our endeavors
to promote good fortune.
[SU-WON]
The longer I look at it,
the more I see
its inherent beauty.
Does it have any monetary value?
No, it's only real worth
is as a lucky talisman.
The true value's in
the iron ore we're mining.
[SU-WON]
Hm.
Well. Nice seeing
you, King Su-Won,
but I've got some important
business to attend to
back in my quarters. If you need
anything, just ask my servants,
they'll be happy
to help you.
[JU-DO]
Hey, come back here!
[CHEOL-RAN] "Important business
to attend to"? Gimme a break.
Thank you.
I look forward to talking with
you again later, General.
Um. 'Scuse me, Your Majesty?
Earlier, when my master was
talking about rising up
in rebellion against King Il,
I'm sure he was only
speaking figuratively.
You know him. He's always trying
to get a rise out of somebody.
So please, don't take
what he said seriously.
He can just get a little
bit crazy sometimes.
There's no need to worry.
I'd never condemn him for it.
No?
Thank you very much for that.
Master Geun-tea
has been depressed
and out of sorts for
a long time now.
His whole sense of
identity revolves around
his reputation as
a mighty warrior.
He doesn't feel quite at home
anywhere but on the battlefield.
I think he resents not being
able to use his skill in war
to save the Kouka
Kingdom from ruin.
He feels helpless
and angry all the time.
He may look rough and callous,
but he truly cares about his
people more than anything.
Yes, I can see that,
the servants demonstrate it.
You can tell they
love him deeply.
[CHEOL-RAN]
Uh?
[SU-WON]
No matter their rank,
everyone here speaks
their mind freely,
without reservation or
fear of being punished.
I think it attests to the
quality of his character.
In that regard, he reminds me
a lot of the people I hold dear.
And you. You love the
general too, don't you?
I couldn't help but notice.
You wear your hair
just like he does.
[CHEOL-RAN chuckles]
And I noticed many
other ponytails, too.
It seems you're not the only one
who holds him in high regard.
No, we all do.
Everyone in the
clan idolizes him.
Can you blame us? His courage
on the battlefield is legendary.
We've all heard stories
of his bravery.
Between you and me,
there was a lot of competition
within the clan to
become his caretaker.
Oh, please promise me
you'll keep that as our
secret, Your Majesty.
If he knew, it'd go
straight to his head.
I don't get what all
the fuss is about.
He's annoying.
I'd like to see him
in action someday.
As brave as everyone
claims him to be,
I imagine it'd be
a remarkable sight.
I know he would love that,
but it might be difficult
since fighting has
been strictly prohibited.
Then, I'm outta luck. Unless...
[CHEOL-RAN]
Master Geun-tea!
You've gotta come
with me right now!
Something incredible's happened,
you're not gonna believe it!
What in the hell are you
yelling about this time, Cheol?
It's King Su-Won!
[GEUN-TEA]
Forget it.
I'm not giving that brat
any more of my time.
Just hear me out, Master!
I spoke with him and...
he wants to go to war!
[GEUN-TEA]
Hm?
King Su-won!
This is the greatest news
ever! I can't believe it!
Don't yell in front of the king!
I'm so excited that you
decided to go to war!
Who's our enemy?
The Sai, Shin, and Kai
could all use a beating!
Ha, ha, ha! This is awesome!
Uh. Leave everything
to me, Your Majesty.
We'll need men and weapons.
General Geun-tea,
I was talking about staging
a mock battle, not a real one.
[GEUN-TEA]
Huh?
I know that you've been longing
for the glory of
the battlefield.
And your people equally yearn
to see you in action once again.
Let's hold a festival
celebrating all of the great
warriors of the Earth Clan!
So, you want all
of my best warriors
to pretend to fight one another.
Yes, doesn't that
sound like fun?
We'll have everyone use fake
weapons on the battlefield.
We don't want anyone
getting hurt.
--[GEUN-TEA growling]
--[JU-DO grunting]
Ju-do, you little sissy boy.
I oughta beat the
crap outta you,
but I suppose it's a good thing
you stopped me from acting out.
I almost lost control of
myself for a second there.
[JU-DO]
How dare you?
You can't attack the king!
I mean, I get it,
he's totally insufferable.
I was just about ready to
teach him a lesson myself.
Your Majesty!
Listen, we've got more
important things to do
than throw a damn festival!
Calm down.
I think you'll actually
enjoy it once the fun begins.
[JU-DO grunts]
I'm excited. Let's make
it one week from today.
Your Majesty.
I'm sorry, but the Earth Clan
has too many troubles
to get wrapped up in this
kind of trivial nonsense.
Perhaps you should
return to your castle.
[CHEOL-RAN]
Oh, man!
So, we're not gonna
do it, Master?
That's too bad, we were looking
forward to having some fun.
You idiots just want an excuse
to slack off and play games!
There's more to it than
them wanting to play.
What?
Oh, General. It's incredible.
You have no idea the power
you hold over them.
[GEUN-TEA]
Huh?
I'd like to visit the men who
were injured in the Udo mine.
Do you think it'd be all right
for me to stop by at some point?
I would be honored
to take you there.
[GEUN-TEA] This is worse
than I could've imagined.
Forget him being
like Master Yuhon,
this man-child's even less
fit to rule than King Il.
My, what lovely tea.
[GEUN-TEA] What's going to
become of my beloved kingdom?
[SU-WON] You're all alone on the
battlefield, General Geun-tea.
If this were a real war,
you would be killed in
a matter of seconds.
So, what'll you do?
Next time on Yona of The Dawn,
Episode 16: "Pretend War."