[GANG TEA-JUN]
Like flames.
It burns like a fire.
I can't tear my eyes away.
She's scorching me.
I've never seen her eyes
burn with such rage.
Idiot!
[HAK]
Didn't I tell you not to move?
Why didn't you listen to me?
He must be a demon.
Princess!
Oh no!
[HAK] Dammit!
The poison is
starting to take hold.
Now's our chance!
Take him out!
Hak!
[GANG TEA-JUN laughing]
Perfect.
Just give him a little push.
The "Lightning Beast" dies now!
[YONA] No, it can't be.
[YONA]
I can't let this happen.
I can't just stand here.
I've got to do something.
I have to stop them.
If I don't...
Hak is... going to die!
Princess!
Don't even think about it!
Oh, I'm afraid not, Princess.
No point in trying
to save him, he's dead.
[GANG TEA-JUN] You are coming
to the castle with me.
Son Hak is going to his death!
[YONA] I have to save him.
Whatever it takes.
I won't let them kill him.
I will not!
[MALE SOLDIER 6G] It's gonna be
such an honor to take you down,
General Son Hak,
the Lightning Beast.
Kohka's greatest warrior!
[YONA] Get away!
I said get away!
Princess...
I'm warning you,
leave Hak alone!
[MALE SOLDIER 6G]
Princess, stop!
Calm down!
You must get a hold
of yourself, Your Highness.
No, stop!
Don't you dare
harm the princess!
But sir!
[MALE SOLDIER 6G] No way.
Is this really the princess?
What are you doing?
[YONA] What's it look like?
I'm trying to save you!
Don't be stupid!
Run away!
You know you can't lift me!
Just run for your life!
[YONA] Shut up! I won't!
[YONA sobbing]
Damn you!
You'd better not die like this!
'Cause I will never forgive you!
Hey!
What are you waiting for?
Get the princess away
from Hak at once!
[YONA screaming]
Master Tea-jun!
[GANG TEA-JUN] Find them.
[MALE SOLDIER 6G] What?
Find them now!
Get out of my sight
and go save the princess!
Master, you have to calm down.
It's futile, they can't have
survived a fall like that.
There's no point in
even trying to save them.
[MALE SOLDIER 6G] Be careful!
Let me go!
Stop this!
I have to save the princess!
[MALE SOLDIER 6G]
Master Tea-jun!
The princess...
She's gone.
Yona... is dead?
[KEISHUK] Master Su-won.
What is it?
Do you need something?
I don't mean to disturb you
on the eve of your coronation.
It's Gang Tea-jun.
He's here, insisting
I let him speak with you.
He seems very upset and
he says it's an urgent matter.
[SU-WON] Ah, Gang Tea-jun.
Sorry to keep you waiting
in the dark like this.
What is it you need
to discuss with me?
Apologies for
insisting you see me now.
It's late, and
tomorrow's the big day.
You're about to become king.
But there's something
I need to give to you,
and I'm afraid it cannot wait.
Please open this.
I'm sorry,
but the princess is dead.
It was an
unfortunate accident.
I didn't mean
for this to happen.
We found her and Son Hak
in the Northern Forest
between our lands and those of
the Wind Clan.
We almost had them,
but they fell over a cliff.
Stop there.
Are you saying that
they fell into the valley?
You knew your orders.
Su-won told everyone to contact
the castle if they were spotted,
but you took matters
into your own hands.
You cornered
and killed them both!
This is nothing
short of high treason!
You will be punished.
[GANG TEA-JUN] You're right.
I killed her.
I murdered the princess.
[GANG TEA-JUN] I beg you.
Please punish me severely.
[KEISHUK] Master Su-won.
[SU-WON] Why don't you
rest here for the evening?
I'd like you to attend the
coronation ceremony tomorrow
as my guest.
Your Highness!
I have to be punished!
I have to! I...
Master Tea-jun!
I beg of you!
Punish me, Your Majesty!
Put me to death!
[BOY singing] Once upon a time,
oh so very long ago,
when the big red sun
was eaten from the sky.
And when darkness
swallowed the whole world.
Man, what a pain.
There goes my evening.
[KEISHUK] Master Su-won.
Elder Mun-deok of the
Wind Clan arrived tonight.
He's accompanied by
the new general-elect.
I just thought you'd
be interested to know.
General-elect?
I suppose they've complied.
[KEISHUK] My feeling is that he
did what he felt was necessary
in order to protect the clan.
Though it does seem rather
uncharacteristic of him.
He's not usually one
to give in so easily.
[SU-WON] I wonder
if he was influenced
by someone to take that path.
A martyr.
One who chose to break
with the clan to save them.
What?
[SU-WON] Nothing.
So, what's your
impression of him?
The Wind Clan's future leader.
Well, for one thing,
it seems he's even
younger than General Hak.
These upstarts
from the Wind Clan
are certainly full
of drive and energy.
You shouldn't express
your envy like that, Keishuk.
It makes you sound old.
I am old compared
to you, "Boy King."
[SU-WON]
Look. It's already dawn.
Ah. Indeed it is.
What a perfect dawn sky for
the morning of your coronation.
[SU-WON] Crimson Dragon Castle.
It's always been a symbol
of Kohka's Kingdom monarch.
I swore that I would
come back here someday.
And here I am,
about to be crowned king.
[YONA] Su-won!
Great to see you!
Welcome back!
Why don't you come up?
There's pear compote!
Hurry and get some
before it's gone!
[HAK] Heads up!
Hi, Hak.
[HAK] You were wide open,
be on guard next time!
You'll get chewed out
by Old Mun-deok
if you don't improve
your speed, buddy.
[SU-WON]
Don't talk such nonsense.
After all,
he's always told me
that I have a natural
aptitude for combat.
[HAK] Is that so?
Then tell me why you've never
beaten me in practice
even since we were kids.
[SU-WON] You're unbeatable.
You have to be in order
to protect Princess Yona,
but that's not
how it is for me.
Some excuse! How lame.
To be honest,
I'm a little jealous of her.
I really wish you
could be my servant.
Come on, you already
have a million of them
all to yourself.
You know they're not the same.
I want you to be mine.
Well, just become king
and I'm yours.
[SU-WON] What?
[HAK] Marry the princess
and ascend to the throne.
Then I'll be your servant, too.
[SU-WON]
Me and Yona? No way!
That'd be like
marrying my sister!
You did say you
wanted me, didn't you?
You know that was
just a figure of speech.
Yeah, but that's
beside the point.
You're the only one I'll support
as next in line after King Il.
When you're king,
I'll always be at your side,
your right hand man.
I'll protect you both.
My life will belong to you
and Yona until I die.
And in return,
I want three meals
and a nap every day.
Put that in my contract.
That's a bargain to own
the "Lightning Beast."
[SU-WON] Yes. As you wish.
I think that'd be
the perfect life.
Su-won, hurry up!
[SU-WON] Hak.
Promise me you'll protect Yona.
[SU-WON] It's sad.
I'm about to be crowned king.
But I can't share this moment
with the two people I love most.
[SU-WON] It's hard not
to question myself.
Have I chosen poorly?
Here I am, King.
Without my right-hand man.
[SU-WON] I trampled over and
threw away a girl who loved me.
Who gave me strength.
Who trusted me,
and believed in me.
[MALE SUBJECT 6A] That can't
be the new king, can it?
[MALE SUBJECT 6B]
He does look like a child,
but he is the only son
of His Highness Yuhon.
[MALE SUBJECT 6A]
Wow, is that really the case?
[MALE SUBJECT 6C] Then there's
no doubt he'll rule the kingdom
better than his predecessor.
[SU-WON] It's done.
Now, let there
be no more doubts.
[NOBLEMAN 6A] With the unanimous
blessing of the five clans,
it is my honor to
stand before you today.
We're gathered to witness
the coronation of King Su-won
as the eleventh ruler
of the Kohka Kingdom!
[ROYAL SUBJECTS gasping]
[GANG SU-JIN]
Congratulations, Your Majesty.
I wish you luck.
Your enthronement is a great
blessing to our nation.
As ruler of the
Fire Clan, Gang Su-jin,
I pledge my undying loyalty
to His Highness Su-won
along with the love and
obedience of all my people.
[SU-WON] The Fire Clan.
They present a
façade of cooperation,
but their hearts
are set on the throne.
[SU-WON] The Earth Clan.
Followers if they
have a strong leader.
[SU-WON] The Water Clan,
watching as things play out.
And finally...
The Wind Clan.
They've submitted
for now under threat of death.
But who knows,
their military is fierce.
Mun-deok trained them well.
Once they hear
of Hak's death,
it'll only be a matter
of time before they rebel.
The Khai in the North,
Shin and Sai in the South.
They are all paying attention
to my enthronement.
But for now...
I have to focus
all of my efforts
on uniting the five clans.
[MUN-DEOK] Your Majesty.
As I'm sure you are
no doubt already aware,
the oracle of
this castle is gone.
That said,
the heavens are still
watching over this kingdom.
I will watch
along with them,
and take note of what
Your Highness builds here,
what he costs his people,
and how he chooses to rule,
before he joins King Il
who came before him
on the other side in death.
Elder Mun-deok!
[SU-WON] I accept that.
I promise I will
always hold you to it,
Elder Mun-deok.
[SU-WON] Just know this.
I have no interest
in the Heavens,
if all they can do
for me is look on idly.
I place all my faith
in the people.
They possess
the guidance I need.
[SU-WON] I will restore this
kingdom to its former glory
as it was under my grandfather,
the ninth ruler, King Junam.
And if anyone stands in my way,
anyone at all,
they will be met by death!
[gasping]
[ROYAL SUBJECTS]
Hurrah!
Long live King Su-won! Hurrah!
[chanting continues]
Elder. Can we go home now?
This whole thing is a real
pain in the butt, ya know?
[MUN-DEOK] He's changed.
I've never seen that ruthless
look in his eyes before.
[YOUNG SU-WON] Master Mun-deok!
Will you watch my spear-fighting
and see if I'm doing it right?
[MUN-DEOK]
That boy who smiled so sweetly.
He's gone, and I'll
never see him again.
[ROYAL SUBJECTS chanting]
[YONA]
Whose voices am I hearing?
So many people.
The chanting of a crowd.
But who is it
they're calling for?
[SU-WON]
...stands in my way,
they will be met by death!
[YONA] Su-won?
Oh, you're awake?
Here, my arms are tired.
Take this.
Don't spit it out.
[YONA] Who're you?
[YUN] My name is Yun.
I'm just a beautiful passerby,
nothing for you
to write home about.
And what about you guys?
Not just anybody could
survive a fall from that cliff.
What cliff?
Oh right, now I remember.
Where's Hak?
What happened to him?
Hak? Oh.
That guy with the black hair
who was with you?
He's right over there.
[YONA] Thank goodness!
Oh, Hak.
He's alive. Barely, though.
I was able to get the
poison out of his system,
but that's a nasty sword
wound he's got on his chest.
Plus the contusions
and broken ribs.
If I hadn't found
you guys when I did,
he totally would have
bled out and died right there.
Ya know...
I think he protected you
when you fell from the cliff.
[YONA] What?
[YUN] He was underneath you
when I found you.
[YONA] Hak.
The trees acted like a buffer
and broke your fall a little.
[YUN] Man, What a pain.
That guy.
He must care a lot about you.
So, boyfriend?
[YONA] Nope. No way.
Wow.
You are cold hearted, lady.
Where are we?
The valley?
Is this where you live?
Yeah, kinda.
So are you a doctor, then?
'Cause I'm looking
for someone in this area,
and you may have treated him--
[MAN] Yun! Where are you?
You're not gonna believe
what just happened to me!
Hey, don't come in here!
Why are you covered
head to toe in mud?
[MAN]
I was praying to the gods
that everyone might
have peace and ease,
and I guess I
kinda got carried away
cause I slipped
and fell in the mud.
[yelling]
Man, what a pain.
The gods have definitely
forsaken you this time!
No!
Oh, you're finally awake!
I'm so relieved!
[MAN] Oh, I'm sorry.
Where are my manners?
My name's Ik-su,
and I suppose I'm what
you'd call Yun's guardian.
Oh, um...
My name is...
[YONA] They seem
like they're trustworthy,
but I think it's still
too soon to tell them.
[IK-SU sobbing]
Sorry, but...
It must have been so painful.
No. It didn't
really hurt that bad.
Hak protected me
when we fell from the cliff.
Good, I'm just so moved
that you were able
to make the journey.
Make the journey?
[IK-SU] It's an honor to have
you stay with us, Princess Yona.
Hold on...
How do you know who I am?
Well, from the
Divine Prophecy of course!
Gah!
[laughs awkwardly]
You're such an idiot.
Did you forget
why we're out here?
It's pointless
if you blurt it out!
Come on! Why can't
you lie just a little bit?
Does that mean you're...
[MUN-DEOK] There's an oracle
who has foretold the future
of the Kohka Kingdom
since ancient times.
Oh. My apologies.
I really wanted
to be dressed properly
when I introduced myself,
but I guess the
gods had other plans!
[YONA] This is the oracle?
This guy? Really?
[IK-SU] The odds were
against you, yet you survived.
As a result, a storm is coming--
one that will turn
the kingdom upside down.
Next time, on Yona of the Dawn,
episode 7: "Fate."