[HAK] I never would've
thought an entire village
was concealed
under this mountain.
[YUN]
I know.
I guess a lot of things aren't
what they appear to
be on the surface.
Ik-su once told me a
story about a village
that fled into a mountain
to escape a horrible war.
Maybe he was talking about them.
Is he here, Gija?
Yes, I'm certain.
I can feel the Blue Dragon.
[YUN, GIJA gasp]
[YUN whimpers]
[GIJA growls]
Who are these people?
[YUN] I'm not sure what to
tell him. What'll we do?
Bring us the Blue Dragon
Warrior at once!
Don't beat around
the bush, Gija.
Blue Dragon, what?
I'm afraid that I have no idea
what you're talking about.
Don't lie to me! The
Blue Dragon is here.
There's no reason to hide him.
His master is
waiting to greet him.
I'm sorry, but I can assure you
there is no "blue dragon" here.
[GROUP gasps]
[ELDER] Is it possible
you have us confused
with some other village?
We are just a humble settlement
without many resources.
We don't want trouble.
I sincerely hope you
haven't come to start any.
That depends.
[YONA]
Please forgive us.
[YONA] We don't mean
to bring you any trouble.
We're merely looking
for a friend of ours.
We're obviously
in the wrong place.
[YONA] However, we're
exhausted from our journey.
And, one of us is injured.
Would it be alright for
us to rest awhile?
Just for one night?
Your journey must've
been a difficult one.
As I'm sure you can see, we
don't have much to offer you.
But, we can certainly provide
you shelter for the night.
[YONA]
That's all we ask.
Thank you very much.
[ELDER]
I'll show you to your quarters.
[YONA gasps]
[YONA]
Why do they wear masks?
[ELDER]
It's an old clan tradition.
Those who are single
cover their faces.
The masks are removed
during a wedding ritual.
[YONA]
What a fascinating custom.
[ELDER] The few visitors
we've had over the years
always have that reaction.
This is where you'll
stay for the evening.
[YONA]
Thank you.
[ELDER]
Oh, and one more thing.
Huh?
The cave system within this
mountain is an intricate maze.
It would be best for
you all to stay put.
We're not responsible,
if anything unfortunate
should befall you.
[YUN] How can we be certain this
is the Blue Dragon's village?
Why do you ask?
I find it odd that nobody
made a fuss about your hair,
especially after the
way everyone reacted
in the White Dragon
Warrior's village.
[GIJA]
Princess, trust me.
I feel the Blue Dragon Warrior.
He's in these caves somewhere.
I know, I would never
doubt your ability.
Uh... Thanks.
I would.
Shut your mouth!
--Well, no sense waiting.
--[GIJA yelling]
We know the Blue Dragon
Warrior's gotta be somewhere
--in this network of caves.
--[GIJA, HAWK yelling]
We're gonna have to
talk to him ourselves.
Let's go while no
one's watching us.
But didn't he say it's like
a labyrinth down here?
What if we get lost?
Oh, come on, Princess.
I'm the Beautiful Boy Genius,
remember? I've got this.
I'll make a map of the caves
like we're in a game!
Find the treasure!
Rifle through all the pots
and closets and drawers!
[YONA, HAK]
Find the stuff!
Find the stu...?
[YUN]
Not another dead end! Damn!
Where are you,
stupid Blue Dragon?
--[YUN grunts]
--[GIJA] He's nearby.
It doesn't add up.
I'm sure he knows I'm here,
why won't he show himself?
Prob'ly 'cause he
thinks you're annoying.
--[GIJA yelps]
--[HAK] Swoosh.
Oh, that's right.
If you feel his presence,
then he can feel yours.
Do you think he's avoiding
us intentionally?
Maybe we should cut
our losses and move on--
[GIJA]
Definitely not!
[YONA, YUN grunt]
We cannot give up on him!
If the Blue Dragon
Warrior's like me,
he's been protecting the
ancient blood his whole life.
He's gotta be waiting for you.
You're his master and he
wants to be reunited with you,
because you need him.
The Four Dragon Warriors were
born to protect you, our master.
All we desire in this
world is to serve you.
My father was the White
Dragon Warrior before me.
Just as I do, he longed
to protect his king,
but he never got the chance.
[GIJA] If the Blue Dragon
could only see you,
he would follow
you in your quest.
[YONA sighs]
Gija.
Hm?
I'm not... the
Crimson Dragon King.
I know.
[GIJA]
Although, I believed you were.
I may not be the king
you've waited for.
[GIJA gasps]
But, I need you.
I want you by my side.
I'm sorry. I'm selfish.
Ohhhh.
Uh. You're way too nice to me.
Lightning Beast, why are
you making that face?
[YUN gasps]
[YUN] Hold on. Something
feels very wrong here.
[YONA]
How so?
[YUN]
This might sound strange.
But it feels like someone's
watching our every move.
Now that you mention
it, I can feel it, too.
[YUN] Maybe the villagers
know we're exploring.
Let's go back.
Yeah.
[squealing]
[YONA gasps]
[YONA]
What was that noise?
[gasps]
[YONA]
A hallway?
--[squeak]
--[YONA gasps]
A squirrel.
[squeaking]
[YONA gasps]
[squeaking continues]
Wait up!
[squirrel squeaking]
[laughs] There you are!
[squeaks]
[YONA laughing]
Oh, you're so cute!
Look, Hak! I found the
cutest little squirrel!
[squirrel squeaking]
[YONA]
Why'd they go out?
Hak?
[YONA]
Gija! Yun!
[gasping]
[YONA]
What should I do?
[STRANGER]
Are you lost, young lady?
Did you get separated
from the rest of your group?
I, uh, well... Yes, I did.
Do you live here?
[STRANGER]
I do. Give me your hand.
[YONA gasping]
[STRANGER] I will show you
the way back to your friends.
Thank you.
[STRANGER]
Didn't the elder warn you
that it's easy to
get lost down here?
[YONA]
Yes, he did.
I should've stayed put,
but I'm looking for someone.
[STRANGER] The Blue
Dragon Warrior, right?
Uh... Yes, sir.
[STRANGER] There's no one by
that name. Not down here.
[YONA] That room
at the end of the hall,
does it belong to someone?
[STRANGER] It's an empty
room. No one's in there.
[STRANGER]
No one at all.
[YONA]
Um, sir?
I don't think this tunnel
is going to lead us
back to my friends.
Why are we going
deeper underground?
[gasps]
[STRANGER grunts]
--[YONA yelping]
--[STRANGER grunting]
Help! Hak!
[gasps]
[STRANGER yelping]
[YONA]
Who is he?
[squirrel squeaks]
[YONA]
He's wearing bells.
And he's got a mask on.
Is he one of the villagers?
[YONA] For some reason,
I feel safe with him.
Dammit! Where did she go?
Any sign?
Why would she
wander off like that?
[GIJA gasping]
He's nearby. I feel him!
[HAK grunts]
[YONA laughs]
[GIJA sighs]
Princess! Where have you been?
--[HAK gasps]
--You dummy!
You're not supposed
to run off, Princess!
I'm sorry, Yun.
You're okay! Thank god!
Yeah, this gentleman
was a big help! Huh?
[GIJA gasps]
[GIJA]
It's you.
Hey, wait!
What's the matter?
He's who we're after.
That was him. The
Blue Dragon Warrior.
[squirrel squeaks]
[squirrel squeaking]
[VILLAGER A]
Are you certain it's true?
The next monster has been born?
[ELDER] Yes.
A baby boy was born
with the Blue Dragon's eyes.
He will grow up to be a
mutant, like the rest of them.
[VILLAGER A]
What happened to the mother?
[ELDER]
She killed herself.
[VILLAGER A]
Who will be charged with caring
for the new Blue
Dragon Warrior?
[ELDER] The former
Blue Dragon, of course.
We must follow the ancient rule.
Never mind that,
hand me the mask.
We must hurry and cover his
eyes before the power awakens.
[BLUE DRAGON]
That was my first memory.
Darkness covering light.
[BOY A]
Ready? Spin it!
Go!
[CHILDREN lauging]
Yes!
Ahh.
[CHILDREN gasp]
[BLUE DRAGON] Uh...
Sorry, but, can I--Can I
please watch you play?
[CHILDREN screaming]
[sighs]
--[AO] Blue Dragon.
--[BLUE DRAGON gasps]
[BLUE DRAGON]
Ao.
[AO]
Come on!
[BLUE DRAGON grunting]
[VILLAGER B]
Huh?
[VILLAGERS gasping, murmurming]
[BLUE DRAGON sighs]
[BLUE DRAGON yelping]
[AO] I told you to stay
here when I'm gone.
You never listen to me!
[BLUE DRAGON]
Sorry... Ao.
It's just...
[BLUE DRAGON] ...all that
I want... is a friend.
Is that right?
So, have you made
any friends yet? Huh?
You're not even close.
Those little jerks don't
want to be friends with you!
[BLUE DRAGON yelping]
[AO] Geez, you're
always getting into trouble.
Sorry.
Hey, Ao?
Do you mind if I ask you
something about the villagers?
[BLUE DRAGON]
Why do they run away from us?
I don't understand.
The power that we have...
is it a curse like they say?
[AO] Anyone who looks into
our eyes turns to stone.
[BLUE DRAGON gasps]
That's what they say.
It's a lie the villagers have
been propagating for centuries.
Our power won't
turn them to stone,
but it paralyzes their
nerves, and in some cases,
it can even stop their
hearts from beating.
It's a frightening power.
It's very dangerous.
[AO] They would kill us
if they thought they could.
[gasps]
[whimpering]
[AO]
Stop crying! You're not cursed!
But I am cursed!
Everybody wants me dead!
[AO]
Yeah, that's right.
Your whole existence is a curse.
Brought upon you
by the Blue Dragon!
Damn it!
I don't know why this ancient
power haunts this village.
One dragon dies,
one takes his place.
Why won't it just
end when we die,
so the people can be free
from the burden of their fear?
[BLUE DRAGON yelps]
But they make up these
lies that do nothing
but make it worse
for themselves!
[AO growls]
[BLUE DRAGON] Ao, people
are coming this way. Bad people.
[AO]
How close?
[BLUE DRAGON] I dunno,
they're sitting around a fire.
And they're looking this way.
[AO] Damn it!
[AO groaning]
[BLUE DRAGON gasps]
Ao!
[AO]
Stay away from me.
[AO groaning]
[BLUE DRAGON]
With every passing day,
Ao's vision grew
weaker and weaker.
My eyes, on the other hand,
continued to gain
strength daily.
It was as if Ao's power was
flowing out of him into me.
[BANDIT A]
Is that the village?
[BANDIT B]
Yeah, apparently there's a guy
who lives there with
some weird powers.
Like a dragon or something.
Whatever.
I'll bet the nobles
would be interested
in a guy with special powers.
He'd probably fetch a high
price if we can capture him.
--[AO] Oh, yeah?
--[BOTH gasp]
[AO] Would I get you
idiots a pretty penny?
[AO]
I hate to disappoint you guys,
but I'm just an
excellent swordsman.
I don't possess
any "special powers."
You who threaten our village.
Sorry your lives were so brief.
Better luck in your next ones.
Ao.
--[AO grunting]
--[BANDITS groaning]
[BLUE DRAGON] He fought well,
even though he couldn't see.
[AO]
Did you watch what I did?
My sword technique?
[BLUE DRAGON]
Yes, sir.
Good. Learn it well,
as quickly as you can.
[YOUNG BLUE DRAGON]
Ao, why do you fight?
With swords, I mean. Why
not just use your power?
That... would be better, right?
--[AO growls]
--[BLUE DRAGON yelps]
Now you listen to me.
Your power is only a curse!
I can teach you to control it,
but you can never use it.
Because if you do, the curse
will come back to haunt you!
You will suffer the same
paralysis you inflict.
It's not worth it
just to win a fight.
--It's a double-edged sword.
--[BLUE DRAGON whimpering]
One that will cut
you if you use it.
Not only that,
but it's also the reason we're
pariahs in our own village.
[grunting]
[BLUE DRAGON] So if, I
never use my power
and I protect the
village with a sword,
do you think...
I'll make friends?
[AO] You can't live
your life that way.
[BLUE DRAGON sighs]
[BLUE DRAGON grunts]
[BLUE DRAGON]
Ao!
Ao. Hold on!
Please, wait! Don't leave me!
[BLUE DRAGON panting]
[BLUE DRAGON grunts]
[BLUE DRAGON groaning]
[gasps]
[BLUE DRAGON] Ao taught
me to fight with a sword.
He taught me how to control
the power of my eyes.
He was strict, but just.
[BLUE DRAGON] Ao became weaker
and weaker as time passed.
[AO groaning]
[BANDIT G yells]
[BANDIT F chuckles]
[panting] Ao!
[BANDIT F grunting]
Dammit!
--[BANDIT F grunting]
--[AO groaning]
Leave!
[BANDIT F yelping]
[AO groaning]
Ao!
Are you all right?
They ran away. Don't worry.
They're gone.
[AO laughs]
[BLUE DRAGON]
Ao?
I'm blind. I can't see anymore.
[laughing]
Finally! I can die in peace!
There isn't any
power left in me!
I can't feel it in my body now!
I'm free to die at last!
I'm human! I can die!
[bells jingling]
[AO]
What's that? A bell?
Have you always worn one?
[BLUE DRAGON]
No, I found it.
I just thought... it
made a pretty sound.
I see.
[AO]
What a great idea.
I'll know where you are, even
if I can't see you anymore.
[BLUE DRAGON gasping]
[AO sniveling]
[AO]
I'm sorry.
[BLUE DRAGON]
Huh?
[AO]
Forgive... me.
I have to--I have to go... away.
I'm so sorry!
[AO crying]
[BLUE DRAGON]
Please, don't leave me, Ao.
Why don't we just talk
about something
else for right now?
All of a sudden, I feel stupid.
I can't think of...
anything else to say.
Why don't you talk instead, Ao?
Please. Say something.
I just wanna hear your voice.
[VILLAGER B] The former
Blue Dragon Warrior died?
[VILLAGER A]
Yes. Finally.
He lasted a lot longer
than those before him.
[VILLAGER C]
So now all the curse resides
within the current
Blue Dragon Warrior.
[bells jingling]
[AO]
What a great idea.
I'll know where you are, even
if I can't see you anymore.
[BLUE DRAGON sobbing]
[BLUE DRAGON]
I'm here! I'm right here!
[BLUE DRAGON grunting]
[BLUE DRAGON] People are
coming. A lot of them.
It seems like a whole army.
[gasps]
[BLUE DRAGON] The bandit
who escaped that night.
He's come back with troops!
What should I do?
I can fight, but there's no
way I can defeat them all.
My mask will give
me away immediately.
What would happen if the
secret of our village got out?
I could put everyone
here at risk.
But, I want to help
them somehow.
[AO]
Your power is only a curse!
--[heartbeat]
--[BLUE DRAGON gasps]
[BLUE DRAGON]
He's right.
My power is what makes
the villagers afraid of me.
It puts them in danger.
I know it's a curse.
I do. But still.
[BLUE DRAGON panting]
[BLUE DRAGON]
The village is my home.
I have to protect it
like Ao always did!
[VILLAGERS gaspsing]
What--What happened
to all of them?
[BLUE DRAGON]
I'm sorry.
I should've listened
to you... Ao.
[BLUE DRAGON]
This power is a curse.
Now I understand why
you told me not to use it.
[squirrel squeaking]
[YONA] So that was the
Blue Dragon Warrior?
[YONA] His touch was
so gentle and warm.
[BLUE DRAGON] What is this
feeling that's come over me?
It feels as if I've been
waiting all my life to find her.
[BLUE DRAGON]
Next time, on Yona of the Dawn,
Episode 13: "The Rippling Fear."