[GIJA]
This feels amazing.
The master I've yearned
for has come at last.
The age-old desire of our clan,
passed down through
the generations.
To all those I left behind
in the village of my birth,
I vow to do justice to our
cause, and protect our ruler.
[HAK]
Hey, Mr. White Snake.
I bet you're tired since
you're not used to travel.
If you call me White
Snake one more time,
I vow to slash your throat!
Anyway, I'm not tired at all.
Oh, really?
I would think you'd at least be
feeling a little homesick.
[GIJA] Nonsense!
My master needs me to
protect her on her journey.
I've gotta protect you, too,
if any danger comes along.
I bet you don't even know how
to fight properly, pretty Boy!
[GIJA, HAK groan]
That's enough of that!
We're going to be spending
a lot of time together,
so no more fighting!
My sincere apologies,
Princess Yona.
[YONA] Hak, this is Gija's first
trip away from his village.
He's nervous, so
leave him alone!
No, I am not nervous!
[YONA] Gija, teasing
people is Hak's hobby.
Don't take it personally!
My hobby?
If you guys are done,
we need to go.
[YONA] Okay!
[BOTH growling]
Hmm...
Gija, you can tell when the
other dragons are nearby?
Your name's Yun, isn't it?
You're right, I can.
If I focus my
mind's eye intently,
I can usually find
my way to them.
In that case, which
one's closest to us?
Let me see.
The Blue Dragon
Warrior is closest.
At least, that's what I feel.
Wow. I'm really impressed
you can sense them. So?
I feel as though...
...he's somewhere over
in that direction.
Uhh... do you think you could
be a little more specific?
Have no fear.
Just follow my lead
and I know we'll find him.
"Have no fear"? How could I not
be afraid of following someone
who's never even been outside?
I may have never been out in the
world, but I do know about it.
My people traveled extensively
and collected data
which I have studied
my whole life.
[GIJA yelps]
[thud]
[YONA, YUN]
Gija!
[GIJA groaning]
[yelps]
No, no no, no!
I don't think I like this!
What are these? They're nasty!
Get me out of here now!
Oh, no, no! Don't do that.
Please get off of me!
Uh?
[GIJA screaming]
[GIJA]
Stop it! Get 'em off me!
How 'bout you just follow us
and watch where you're
stepping from now on?
Ugh. I can still feel
their nasty little legs
crawling all over my body.
So, the White Dragon Warrior's
no match for some little bugs.
[GIJA]
Shut up!
I just don't like the idea of
slimy, creepy crawly things
getting all over my body!
My power was bestowed upon me,
not by some human, but
by the proud White Dragon!
So, show some
respect, you mongrel!
[gasps]
Look, another centipede!
Oh, no, no, no, no, no!
Well, doesn't matter
to me one bit.
I'm not gonna count
on some dusty old dragon
power to protect us.
Say what? You want to put
it to the test, you jerk?
Let's go.
[BOTH gasp]
Princess, go hide, now.
[YONA]
But why?
What's the matter, Gija?
Someone's coming.
Who do you think it could be?
Well, it seems like
a whole lot of 'em.
By the sound of their footsteps,
they're a pretty rough bunch.
Wha--? Oh, no!
We're really close to
the Fire Clan territory!
Are we enemies of the Fire Clan?
Yeah. I'd say mortal enemies.
Hey, Hak! You gonna
let me shoot my bow?
Nope, you're not ready yet.
Just hide and stay quiet.
[YONA groans]
Come on, let's go.
Oh, wow. It looks like we
hit the jackpot today, boys.
No way, these
jerks don't look like
they have anything good on 'em.
Ah, they're nothin' but bandits.
I wouldn't call that nothing.
They've got somethin'. Two
beautiful girls over there.
[YONA gasps]
I'm a beautiful boy, you jerk.
This guy's got some nice clothes
and a good-looking face.
I bet he'd fetch a high price.
Hak, it's not a problem
if I slash this guy, right?
No, but you can run
away if you want to.
Not a chance.
Hm? What's the matter, Pretty
Boy? Shakin' in your shoes?
All ya gotta do is keep quiet.
If you don't want to die, keep
your mouth shut and do exactly--
[groaning]
[yelps]
What'd he do to you?
Well, I don't really know.
His arm is hot! It burned my
skin when I grabbed him!
What? Quit screwin' around!
[heartbeat]
Don't just assume that you
can put your hands on me.
[BANDITS grunting]
This power?
It's been waiting to protect its
master for thousands of years.
Even I have no control over it!
What the...?
No way!
Look at his arm!
The wait is over,
arm of the White Dragon!
[GIJA yelling]
[BANDITS yelping, groaning]
This guy's a monster!
[GIJA grunting]
[BOTH gasp]
[HAK] Now I see the strength
of the dragon's claws.
You fight a lot nastier than
your face suggests.
My arm. It wants more.
Maybe I should protect you.
That's what the
princess wants, right?
I'd be happy to lend a hand.
Thanks, but I've got it.
I can protect myself.
You don't know
who you're dealing with!
[yelling]
[BANDITS yelping, groaning]
[BANDIT R yelps, grunts]
Who the heck are you guys?
This isn't normal!
That was rude. And inaccurate.
White Snake's the
only abnormal one.
[yelps]
[HAK] Who're you trying to slash
with that thing, me or them?
What did I tell you about
calling me White Snake?
I vowed to slash your throat.
Don't take it personally.
It's just my "hobby."
All teasing aside,
don'tcha think you're
getting a little too excited?
That thing's swollen.
Perhaps I'm more committed
to protecting the
princess than you.
And just so you know...
...your weapon gets in my way!
[BOTH grunt]
You Dragon Warriors
sure are dedicated.
Why don't you tell
me your reason
for protecting the
princess so intently?
[chuckles]
I'm not getting personal with
some idiot that I just met.
--[gasps]
--[BANDIT yelling]
What did you call me?
[HAK]
Stay focused!
[BANDITS yelping]
[GIJA] It's insane. I thought
he was a weak human,
but his strength, it's...
like nothing I've ever seen.
I hate to admit it, but he's as
strong as my dragon's arm.
This is unreal! They're gods!
Gija's strength and Hak's
speed are unbeatable!
No enemy could possibly
stand a chance. It's amazing.
[YUN]
Do you wanna help them?
[gasps]
Hak told me to hide and stay
quiet. So, no.
But, isn't this
the kinda situation
you've been practicing for?
[YONA grunts]
Based on my calculations,
you can shoot far enough to do
some real damage from here.
[BOTH grunting]
[YUN] Aim for the guy
behind that tree.
Point just a little bit higher.
Now, shoot 'im!
[BANDIT yelps, yells]
Success!
Wow, thanks, Yun! You're a
much better teacher than Hak!
I can teach you
the ropes any day.
When I tried myself,
it's not so good.
[YONA yelping]
[YUN gasps]
Keep your mouths shut
and don't move, girls.
You'll make such
pretty little hostages.
[grunts]
[YONA yelping]
--[GIJA] Whoa. Close one.
--[HAK] Hey. You okay?
Thanks, you guys.
Gimme a break.
[YONA]
So, is it over?
How many of those
guys did you take out?
Huh? Oh, I never keep track.
Well, I took down 28.
Then I must've got 40.
Dirty liar! You just told
me you never keep track!
Besides, there weren't
that many to begin--
--[heartbeat]
--[GIJA yelps]
[GIJA groaning]
Gija! Are you... okay?
[GIJA] Yes. I'm sorry.
I guess I overdid it.
I wanted my fighting to
impress you, so I went all out.
But I got carried away.
Oh, really? I thought
it was about right.
Your fighting style is
better than anyone
who's ever fought beside me.
It makes me happy.
I've found an equal.
Finally, someone who's worthy
of standing beside me in battle.
One day, you and
I should... spar.
[YONA] Hak!
Did he just die?
He's not dead!
[YUN] What an idiot!
He reopened his wounds!
He really hasn't healed
enough to be fighting.
He acts like a god,
but he's human after all.
[GIJA] He fought so well
and with that kind of injury?
Unbelievable. This guy...
He's a monster.
I doubt he'd appreciate
that, coming from you.
[YUN]
It's gonna be getting dark soon.
We need find a place
to bed down for tonight.
Do you know of a
lodge around here?
No, we're gonna camp out.
Outside?
[sighs] Yeah, that's
usually how it works.
Look, just follow
closely behind us
and try not to get scared, okay?
[YONA grunting]
What do you think
you're doing, Princess?
He's out cold. Someone
needs to carry him.
I thought that I could help--
Wow, thanks, Gija!
It's no big deal.
My dragon's arm's ten times
stronger than a normal person's.
[YONA, YUN gasp]
Wait. Hold on. That arm
doesn't have special powers.
Don't worry about him.
He's gonna be fine.
What?
He always makes it through.
It's just that... my whole
life he's been my protector.
Someday I wanna
return the favor.
You're remarkably strong
for a young girl who
grew up in a castle.
No way, that's not true!
How can you say that
when you stayed so calm
in the face of those bandits?
You're right, but
bandits don't scare me.
After seeing my father
killed that night,
not much frightens me.
[YUN] Hey!
Hurry up!
[YONA chuckles]
Let's go.
[GIJA]
This feeling.
I can't get over this desire
to protect my master.
Is it because of
the dragon's blood?
I feel the need to care for her.
She is strong, but there's
a vulnerability she's hiding,
and it stirs
something within me.
Uh... What is this?
It's what's for dinner
tonight. Something wrong?
Yes, there is!
This is not a meal,
it's just a bunch
of boiled weeds
you picked from
the side of the trail!
They are not just weeds! They're
nutritious, edible wild plants!
If you don't shut your mouth,
next time you're eating insects!
Insects? You don't
actually eat bugs, do you?
They have a lot
of nutritional value.
[GIJA]
Princess, do you mean to tell me
you're okay with
eating like this?
I can't stomach eating bugs yet,
but I've gotten used to
pretty much everything else.
I mean, after all,
it's not as though I had
much choice in the matter.
But, thanks to Yun's
amazing cooking skills,
our meals are much
tastier than you'd think!
If you had seen some of the
stuff that Hak made me eat--
Gija, what are you
crying about now?
I feel so sorry for you.
I can't believe the
hardships you've endured.
[HAK] What was that you
said about my cooking?
Oh, Hak. Glad you're awake!
I'm not letting that one slide.
Are you feeling any better?
I'm fine.
Don't change the subject.
Would you care to repeat what
you said about my cooking?
Your cooking?
I said it was great!
So, I'll bet you're hungry!
I see someone's gotten
better at deflecting.
Do you think that you can move?
Better yet, I'll go
get you some food.
Here, now open your mouth.
Ahhhh. Ah?
I've got this.
You don't need to sully
yourself with tedious errands.
White Snake, we were
having a moment.
You've got some nerve, trying to
get the princess to feed you.
[YUN] Okay, now that
we're done with dinner,
let's talk about the
Blue Dragon Warrior.
Gija, do you sense his presence?
I feel something that way.
Right, thanks again
for being so helpful.
Do you know if he lives in a
protected village like you did?
Or is he on his own?
I don't know for sure,
but I've heard things.
According to the intelligence
our scouts brought back
to my village, the Blue Dragon's
people used to live in hiding
within the Earth
Clan's territory.
One day the village
disappeared into thin air.
No one saw or heard from
any of the villagers
or the Blue Dragon ever again.
They disappeared?
But they've gotta be alive
out there somewhere!
[GIJA] Hmm...
If I concentrate hard enough,
I can definitely feel the
Blue Dragon's heartbeat.
Ik-su did mention the
other dragons were nomadic.
So, then, what I bet they did
is move the whole
village into hiding.
You've been pointing
towards North-North East,
straight into
Fire Clan territory.
There are about six locations
that could potentially
hide a village like that.
Yun, have you been there before?
No, I haven't, but still.
I do know there are a few
large towns just past Saika.
This area up here is
used for trade routes.
It's also where a
lot of noblemen
have their second homes.
By process of elimination,
I can surmise there are
only six other areas
out of the way enough
to hide a whole village.
You are smart!
You're the cutest little
"boy genius" I know!
Ugh, stop treating me
like a little kid!
You're only a year
older than me.
That's enough chit chat!
Tomorrow, our Blue Dragon
hunt will start in earnest!
Goodnight, sleep tight,
and all that junk.
Yeah, sleep well--
Wait, out here?
Good night, sweet dreams.
Wait. Wha--
Oh, can it, White Snake!
No.
[GIJA]
So tired.
Gija!
What in the world happened
to your beautiful face?
Oh, sorry for my hideousness.
Ohh, look at that, there's a
centipede on your back.
[GIJA yelping]
[YONA]
Calm down!
H-He was just messing
with you! I swear!
I don't know how much longer
I can handle these guys.
Listen up, we're entering
a town, so try to blend in.
We're in the heart of
the Fire Clan's domain.
Try to play it cool!
[ALL] 'Kay.
[YUN]
This'll never work.
Well, Gija?
I don't sense him here.
Wouldn't want it to
be too easy, right?
Looks like the next stop
is 24 miles from here.
No, wait, that
one's off the list.
The Fire Clan turned it
into a military training camp.
Huh?
Okay, what about this place?
[HAK] There's a lot
of military there, too.
[YUN] Yikes. I guess
we should avoid it, then.
Gija, is something wrong?
No.
Okay, you guys.
We've got it figured out.
There's only three options.
One of them's gotta
be the village.
Uh, really?
You've got some good
intel, Lighting Beast. Wow.
Well, I was one of the
five generals, after all.
It was our duty to keep abreast
of the other clans'
military movements.
I wanna hear about that!
[HAK]
Sure. Let's talk.
[YUN]
'Kay. Move out.
Nothing?
Nope.
He's not around here.
Here, either.
[YONA, YUN, HAK groan]
[HAK, YUN groan]
[YUN]
Well? Anything?
[GIJA] No.
--[YONA, HAK sigh]
--This is getting ridiculous!
[GIJA]
Something's pulling me that way.
[YUN]
You mean we have to go farther?
It's so strange. He's not in
any of the places we predicted.
I guess it's possible
he could'ave crossed
the border, but still.
Maybe your nose is stopped up
or something, White Snake.
I'm not some dumb
dog following a scent!
Princess. I hope you
didn't hurt your feet.
[YONA] Oh, It's okay.
I'm just tired from walking.
Here, drink this.
Oh, wow! That's delicious!
That's homemade fruit wine.
It's good for soothing fatigue.
I'll wrap up your
feet in hot herbs
so you can rest for the evening.
You're the best, Yun.
Your wonders never cease.
[GIJA]
I don't get it.
How can anyone sleep out
in the open like this?
[GIJA]
Everyone is so exhausted.
We've been on the road for days.
Hiding, traveling off
the beaten path.
If only my senses
were more acute,
I could pinpoint the Four
Dragons more easily.
Then the princess wouldn't have
to be suffering such fatigue.
Having to rely on Yun and Hak
it makes me feel so helpless.
[grunts]
[GIJA]
Blue Dragon Warrior.
My brother of the
same sacred blood.
I know you're out there.
Your master, she's
calling for you,
longing to be reunited with
you after all these centuries.
I know you must feel
the same desire to serve
and protect her once more.
[GIJA] I guess I must
have fallen asleep.
[thud]
[GIJA] What's that?
[GIJA]
It's the princess.
But why at this hour?
Princess--Mm.
Don't interrupt her.
[GIJA] How long has she
practiced archery?
Since before we met you.
Every chance she gets.
200 arrows a night, or more.
200--?
Keep your voice down.
[GIJA] Why is she
pushing herself so hard?
It's not as though she'll
ever have to fight
with me here to protect her.
[HAK] I dunno. Doesn't
really make sense.
'Cause she doesn't have
to worry with me around.
But still, she seems ashamed of
her helplessness sometimes.
[GIJA gasps]
[HAK] Her father was killed.
She's without a home.
The only thing she wants
in this world is to survive.
She knows she can't do it on
her own and it eats away at her.
This is how she
takes back power.
Don't you think you
should stop her?
Weapons aren't
meant for princesses.
Do you think I that
want to see her fight?
It's the last thing
I would ever want.
But I do wanna
see her struggle.
Pain is a teacher.
Through pain we grow.
[GIJA] Ughh. Die, die,
die, you nasty bug!
Get away from me!
[grunts]
[GIJA] If only I could
do what she needs.
All I want is to be
of service to her.
My whole life he's
been my protector.
Someday I wanna
return the favor.
[GIJA] That's right. She
feels the same thing I do.
[GIJA]
Today is going to be the day
I find the Blue Dragon Warrior.
Gija, did you get any sleep?
Huh? Yeah. I guess.
You don't sound too sure.
It's hard to adjust
to living outside
when you've slept in
a bed your whole life.
Take care of yourself.
You're very important
to our mission.
If you're not okay,
then neither are we.
[gasps]
Thank you, Princess.
Though, I'm curious.
Am I actually helping,
or am I really a burden?
[chuckles] Don't be silly.
You are indispensable, Gija.
[GIJA gasps]
[GIJA] What's this?
My heart is pounding.
Is the dragon's blood
in my veins getting
all riled up again?
I've got it!
What?
The Blue Dragon's Village, of
course ! It just came to me!
I assumed it was uninhabitable,
but people actually live there!
It's a town on the border.
Deep within that mountain.
[YONA]
Blue Dragon. I'll find you.
[YONA] So that was the
Blue Dragon Warrior?
His touch was so
gentle and warm.
[YONA]
Next time, on Yona of the Dawn,
Episode 12:
"The Blindfolded Dragon."