I thought perhaps
I'd find you in here.
[gasps]
[KEISHUK]
As you suspected, your Majesty,
we found two sets
of accounting books.
The evidence we gathered
supports your theory of
fraudulent tax administration.
Thank you for your work.
We have removed the
administrator in question,
but I'm afraid,
the corruption runs deeper
than we originally thought.
King Il was an
extremely kind man.
While that's not a crime in
itself, it can lead to trouble.
People mistake kindness
for weakness.
Too often humanity's greed will
lead them to take advantage.
Indeed.
Your Grace, isn't that
book one of those
which your father forbade
during King Junam's rule?
[SU-WON]
Yes.
It's the legend of
the Four Dragons.
When I was a little boy,
I used to sneak in here.
This book was my favorite,
partly because it was forbidden.
[SU-WON] But, it's only
a story. A fairy tale.
No fictional god is coming
to save the kingdom.
We, the people,
must work to rebuild it.
[MERCHANT]
Long time no see, kid.
I've been desperate
for your medicine.
I'll trade you for some
rice if you've got it.
[MERCHANT]
Yeah.
I've never seen you travel
with friends before.
You're usually alone.
So, uh, who's the big
guy with the stick?
Well...
[HAK] Just a fellow
traveler on the road
on route to the border
on a delivery.
Pleased to meet you, sir.
[HAK]
Princess.
Princess!
What're you so mad about?
The indignity of being
a bag of clothes?
Look, I had to handle you
roughly so it'd be believable,
I even warned you beforehand.
Okay, I'm sorry I took
advantage of the situation
and grabbed your butt.
You'll pay for that!
How dare you?
It was already a
scary situation...
I thought that guy
was onto us for sure,
my heart was pounding
the whole time!
Okay, listen up, you guys.
Princess Flame Head
of the Morning!
And ex-general Wildebeest!
Lightning Beast.
And I'm a Beautiful Boy Genius!
We gotta lay low, 'cause
the three of us stick out.
We're near Fire Clan land, and
the royal capital, so heads up.
You know what happens
if we're caught, don't you?
[YONA, HAK]
Yeah.
And, thanks to the oracle,
we also know that the
Four Dragon Warriors
all live in extremely
remote locations.
Do you have any leads? Where can
we find these Dragon Warriors?
Well, the four who inherited the
dragons' blood live separately,
they're scattered
throughout the kingdom,
and they're constantly
moving around,
so it's difficult to get a good
bead on their exact locations.
[BOTH]
What a pain!
But I do know where
one of them lives!
Ever since the days of the
legend, one clan has lived
on a foggy mountain top
protecting the blood-line.
They have kept to
themselves for centuries,
living independently
from all other clans.
They don't usually
accept outsiders,
so you'll have to be very
persuasive to get their help.
[HAK]
They live near the border, huh?
[IK-SU]
Yes. It's going to be dangerous
crossing through Fire Clan lands
and near the royal capital.
If that wasn't bad enough,
we're passing the Khai Empire.
I've never seen much
of the world,
so a secret village
is super exciting!
It's gonna be great!
Then, I'm gonna start
writing a travel-log
about seeing the whole kingdom!
Oh, yeah? Your eyes,
why are they all puffy?
[YUN yelps]
[HAK]
You can always go back home
if you miss the
oracle that much!
We don't want you with us if
you're gonna cry the whole time!
[YUN]
You shut your mouth!
Someone's coming!
[sighs]
It's fine. Your injuries haven't
finished healing, and I don't
want you to feel like you have
to carry me all the time, Hak.
[HAK grumbles]
Anyway, I wanna
see the kingdom.
I've been sheltered
my whole life.
Fine, have it your way,
but let's not forget what
Yun said about this area.
It may look safe,
but you can never tell,
so we have to
stay on guard. Huh?
Hey, Yun! What's that thing?
[YUN]
Wow, that's a giant waterwheel!
I've never seen one that big!
[sighs]
[YONA] How pretty.
What's that they're growing?
[HAK] Wheat. It looks like
they've got some rice, too.
[YUN] It's because this area
is so close to the capital.
I'm willing to bet this is where
they grew most, if not all,
the food you ate as you were
growing up in the castle.
It came from these crops?
[BOY laughing]
[BOY, MOM laughing]
Mom, I did it!
Let me see, love!
Oh, you did such a good job!
[BOY, MOM laughing]
[MOM]
I'm so proud of you!
Hm. That's almost
everything we need.
I'm still concerned
it's not enough,
seeing as we don't know when
we'll be able to restock.
But it's the best
we can do for now.
Yeah.
Hak, what are you
so worried about?
Did you forget to pick up
something we need?
Uh. Sort of.
[YONA sighs]
You can go if you want to.
We'll wait here.
We won't talk to anyone
while you're gone.
It'll be fine. This seems
like a quiet village.
These are good people,
and I haven't seen
signs of any troops.
If anything feels off,
you start running, okay?
Don't hesitate,
just get outta here.
And rendezvous at the big tree,
like we discussed earlier.
Stick to the plan.
I'll be right back.
[HAK] I was able to find
the glaive and spear,
but I lost the bow somewhere
in the Northern Mountains.
[HAK] Huh?
That one's for self defense.
It's light enough for a girl,
but make no mistake, it can
kill a grown man easily.
I have no need for it.
Defense is my job, not hers.
Huh?
[VILLAGER A]
Really?
I had heard that a new
king had been crowned,
but I brushed it off as
a rumor. It's true then?
Yes. Apparently he's incredibly
young and good-looking,
and he says he wants
to change things.
But, he's the son of
Prince Yuhon the war hero.
I wonder if he's...
[YONA]
I see.
So, Mun-deok did it, then.
He approved Su-Won's ascension
to the throne, after all.
I'm glad.
Hopefully, that
means the Wind Clan
will be out of harm's way now.
Hey, what's the matter?
Are you okay?
[YONA grunts]
[YONA]
Mh-hm.
Su-won is king.
He murdered my father and
now he lives in the castle
that was once my home.
Uhh... Are you listening?
[STOREKEEPER]
Excuse me, miss.
Would you care for
another cup of tea?
Uh, no, thank you. I'm fine.
Excuse me, please.
Wait! Stop! Come back!
Thanks a lot. Have a good day.
Uh, thank you, sir.
What got into you
all of a sudden?
Try to not do anything that
raises unnecessary suspicion.
[BOTH gasp]
Hurry! This way!
[YUN] Guess I was wrong
about the troops.
They must've been
away at the capital.
And they're just
now coming back.
Hey!
[VILLAGER D]
Oh, hello there!
When did you guys
get back from Kuhto?
Just a few hours ago.
Wow, that recently?
[SOLDIER]
The capital was spectacular.
[VILLAGER D] I bet!
[SOLDIER]
There were people everywhere
and all this exotic food.
I'm telling you,
it was a great party!
[sighs]
[YONA sighs]
[YONA yelps
[grunts]
[SOLDIER]
There were people everywhere
and all this exotic food.
[sighs]
[YONA sighs]
[YONA yelps]
Please, Princess. Stay quiet.
Let's go. No sense in staying.
[HAK] I'm sorry.
I didn't think it through.
I shouldn'ta left you two
alone, not even for a minute.
No. It's my fault.
I'm sorry.
[FARMER A] They're saying the
tax situation will get better
now that we have a different
king in the capital.
[FARMER B]
Don't get your hopes up.
It doesn't matter
who sits on the throne,
royalty will never understand
the hardships of the
people they rule over.
[YUN sighs]
Hoofing it uphill is a lot
harder, but at least we don't
have to worry about being
noticed all the way out here.
We have to stay alert.
The Fire Clan could
be patrolling the area,
so we can't let our guard down.
[YUN sighs]
I'm helpless. I wanna fight.
With a sword.
Hak, you said you would
teach me how to protect myself.
No, I never said that.
Uh...
We don't have to take
time out of traveling.
Teach me how to defend
myself against attackers.
[HAK]
Princess...
Do you think you're capable
of killing someone?
[gasps]
[HAK]
You say you wanna fight,
but attackers don't give in so
easily and they don't run.
You have to be ready to kill,
or, at the very least, injure
them because they won't relent.
When we were cornered
on the cliffs of the
Northern Mountains,
it was the first time I was
forced to pick up a sword.
And I didn't know
what to do with it.
[YONA] I may not be able
to kill someone right now,
or even injure them.
But I want to have the ability
to buy us some time to get away.
That's all.
I suppose it's not a bad idea.
[YONA]
Will you teach me?
I'll make you a deal.
[YONA]
The bow?
[HAK]
I'll fight on the front lines.
You stay back and pick off
our enemies off with this.
Okay. But, I want a sword, too!
[HAK] Archery's all I'm
gonna teach you for now.
[YONA growls]
Listen to me.
King Il hated weapons.
He forbade you from
ever using them.
And right now,
I'm disobeying his orders.
[HAK] I want you to consider
why he hated violence
and keep that in mind
when you use this.
[YUN]
I'm curious.
How do you plan to
teach her archery
while we're climbing up
mountains every day?
[HAK]
I dunno.
If we weren't traveling, I'd
make her shoot 200 arrows a day
until she got the hang of it.
200?
I guess we can start
by shooting at birds
and rabbits as we travel.
That sounds great!
Then we won't have
to worry about dinner!
And now you can pull
your weight, Princess.
[YONA yelps]
[YONA groans]
Hak, I can't hit any of them.
What do you think
I'm doing wrong?
[thunk]
[thud]
Just do that.
I didn't see what
you did differently.
I aimed.
Sorry, I don't get it.
Get what?
[YUN] A natural can't
understand the feelings
of those who can't do it.
[YONA] Hak, you're a terrible
teacher, you know that?
[HAK]
Well, you're a terrible student!
You're not strong enough.
Practice until you can pull
the string back firmly
without shaking.
Once it's in your muscles
it'll come to you naturally.
You got it?
Now, watch how it's done.
It's all sensed in the body.
An expert can hit any target
without even looking.
Just don't make the mistake of
letting your vision fool you.
For now, how 'bout
you focus your energy
on building strength
and shooting straight?
[sighs]
[YONA grunting]
Ugh. Who's making
all that racket?
[YONA grunts]
[YUN] She's practicing archery
in the middle of the night?
[gasps]
[YUN] Today's breakfast is
wild bird and rice with veggies!
It looks delicious!
I'm so amazed by everything
that you can do, Yun!
[YUN]
Well, I am a genius, after all.
I saw you practicing.
You're getting better
at drawing your bow.
Really? You're an
archer, too? No way!
I know my way around
a bow and arrow.
But I don't like
carrying weapons.
It's not something you
should do half-heartedly.
[YONA]
Huh?
I'm talking about the idea
of taking another life.
You're learning for
self-defense,
but people like you
and I can't afford
to show any mercy
on the battlefield.
We have to kill or be killed.
In order for us to survive,
we have to land a single blow
to a vital point
and kill instantly.
If not, we have to use
our brains to get out.
The only reason
Hak can hold back
is because he's the
Lightning Beast.
We're not like him,
and we never will be.
[boar squeaking]
[YONA]
It's so cute.
If I'm going to survive
on the battlefield,
I have to kill humans,
and I don't even want
to hurt this boar.
To draw this bow means
being willing to take a life,
or else have my own
life taken from me.
[boar squealing]
[gasps]
[YONA] Father hated the pain
of violence more than anything.
I'm sorry, Father.
But in order to survive,
I must learn to take a life.
I must learn to kill.
You almost got it.
I just hurt it for nothing.
That's even more cruel.
You missed because
you hesitated.
[gasps]
Yun, you can go on without us.
All right, but don't linger.
We're almost to the
place Ik-su mentioned.
I know, we'll catch up with you.
[HAK]
Okay, it's time.
You must now show your skills
so your master can judge
your improvement.
Right! First, you
must hit this tree.
Nicely done, Princess!
I'm impressed!
You can hit a motionless tree!
Oh, thank you.
I feel so much better.
'Kay, let's see.
For your next target...
Here. Aim it right at me.
[YONA]
Uh. No way!
[HAK]
It'll be fine. I can dodge it.
[HAWK] This will teach you
how to hit moving targets.
No, this will teach
you how to hit people.
I'm going to move around a lot.
You just try and shoot me.
I can't be held responsible!
[HAK grunts]
[YONA]
How'm I supposed to shoot you
when you jump around like that?
[HAK]
Sorry, but people move.
Try harder. You're not
even comin' close.
[gasps]
You're not bloodthirsty enough.
[YONA] What? Why would
I be bloodthirsty?
I'm shooting at you!
[HAK] Then in that case,
pretend I'm not me.
Imagine me as one
of those soldiers
on the mountain that day.
It won't work.
I don't want to kill.
All right. Try this.
Imagine I'm Su-won
and shoot at me.
[YONA gasps]
I hate this side of
you, Hak. I really do.
[YONA]
But in spite of that,
I would still take
a life for you.
I'm willing to
take up a weapon...
..if it means I can
protect you from harm.
[YONA]
Hak?
Don't say that...
about protecting me.
What do you mean?
I'll want more.
[YONA]
Hm?
And anyway, it's my
job to protect you.
[YONA gasps]
[HAK] I told you that I want
you to think of me as a tool.
You don't have to worry about
protecting tools, do you?
The visibility seems
to be getting worse.
Strange. I thought we'd
catch up to Yun by now.
A secret mountain village
shrouded in fog.
It's supposed to be around here,
but I see no sign of it.
[YONA]
Oh, no! Come quickly!
I can't see anything!
Where are you?
[YONA]
I'm over here! Please, hurry!
Look, Hak, this stuff. These
are Yun's things, aren't they?
Yun! Where are you?
Please answer me!
[gasps]
[VOICES]
Leave! Leave!
[OLD MAN] Depart this place
immediately and do not return!
Who are you?
[OLD MAN A]
If you come one step farther,
you will incur swift
divine punishment.
Who makes a threat
while hidden behind mist?
What kind of cowardly gods
can't punish their
enemies face-to-face?
Just who are you people?
I've never seen anyone
clear the fog. It's unreal.
First, tell us. Are you
from the Dragon Village?
[MAN B] How do you
know about our clan?
Who sent you here?
[OLD MAN] Your knowledge alone
gives us reason to kill you.
There was a boy here earlier.
Were you all traveling together?
We won't answer till
you tell us where he is.
What did you do with him?
Like you, he trespassed--
No, it can't be!
She has crimson hair.
Just like the legend.
Is she the one?
But she's a young girl.
[OLD MAN grunts]
[OLD MAN] Please,
tell us truthfully, Miss.
Where are you from
and why are you here?
From Fuga. The oracle told
us we would find you here.
We're seeking out the
Four Dragon Warriors.
Are you the one who carries
the White Dragon's blood?
Huh?
The oracle sent you?
No, Miss. I'm not the dragon,
but I'm one of those
charged with his protection.
[gasps]
[OLD MAN]
Allow us to guide you to him.
We will lead you to
the White Dragon's Village.
[WHITE DRAGON] The Dragon's
blood flows through my veins.
It cried out when
I first saw you.
I've been waiting
for you, my master!
Next time, on Yona of the
Dawn, Episode 10: "Yearn."