Look at that energy field!
Why is there so much of it
concentrated in this one place?
Gives me the creeps.
A remote stronghold
left from a Golden Age...
The Nobles call it...
the Lost City.
...and Jaguara controls it.
Her keep is somewhere
inside there, huh?
[CHER] What do you intend
to do with Cheza?
[CROWD chattering]
[chattering continues]
[GUARD] Don't stop,
keep the line moving.
That's it.
[beeping noise]
[GUARD]
Sorry, Sir. Come with me.
Hey... what seems
to be the problem here?
[QUENT]
So... it was this...
[TOBOE]
Wow! It's so warm!
[HIGE] See? Boy, when
I'm right, I am so right!
Right?
You forgot to mention...
It stinks here.
Stop complaining.
How'd you know about this?
Hmm... Can't say for sure...
Hey, must be my keen instinct.
Instinct, huh?
[TOBOE]
Look how high the ceiling is!
Man, I've never seen
a dome this big before.
[TSUME]
So what's the plan?
Cheza's gotta be
somewhere in the keep.
Hmm... Well...
If that's the case,
it should be over there.
How d'you know that?
[stomach growling]
[HIGE]
Uh...
Hey, why don't we
break up into teams?
You guys look for
a way in or somethin'
and the runt and I will
scope out the joint, 'kay?
Don't you mean
scope out the food?
[HIGE laughs]
Don't worry.
We'll be sure to bring back
enough for everyone.
Right?
Mm-hmm!
Leave it to us!
We would be less
conspicuous if we split up.
All right.
The two of us'll go and check
out the area around the keep.
It's a plan.
We'll meet you
back here at moonrise.
[TOBOE]
Hige, wait for me!
[BLUE] I gotta bad feeling
about this place...
Doesn't it feel like
we're being watched?
[CHER]
Maybe the keep is up there.
It looks like you can't get
into the city without an ID.
[BLUE] Well, then I guess
we'd better get some.
Easier said than done.
What do you suggest?
[BLUE]
Hmm...
[BOY 1]
Hello, ladies!
Damn! You're fine!
See? Didn't I tell ya
they were hotties?
[CHER]
Hey, can I ask you something?
Sure! What do you wanna know?
Do you boys... have any IDs?
Well can't ya tell
by lookin' at us? Hmm?
See ya round, fellas.
[BOY 1]
Snap! Oh, that's cold!
Don't be like that!
Check it, man!
This one's even younger
and prettier than the blond!
[CHER]
Come on.
[BOY 1]
Wait a second!
Let go!
[BOY 1]
What's your damage?
It won't kill ya to have
a little fun, will it?
Hands off.
[BOY 1 laughs]
Oh, man, I love your eyes.
You got us both
shakin' all over!
If you don't
get lost right now,
you're gonna regret it.
You got it wrong, babe.
I don't regret nothin'!
[BOTH yell]
Are you okay?
Yeah.
[BOY 1]
Oh yeah!
Hoowee, are you strong!
I'm all weak in the knees!
[BOY 1 laughs]
[BOY 1]
Catch ya later!
What was that about?
Who knows...
Thank you, Blue.
Those boys didn't
know what hit 'em.
You're amazing.
They were kids.
Anyway, you have some
pretty amazing weapons
of your own, you know.
[CHER]
Huh?
Y'got brains,
and guts and the
wiles of a woman.
[laughing]
[BOTH laughing]
[TOBOE] We should be able
to find food and water
and just about anything else
in a place like this,
don'tcha think?
After you turn
the corner up ahead,
there's a big stairway
that leads up.
After that...
What are you talking about?
It's really here...!
Hige, what's going on?
[BOY 1]
Yeah!
You morons!
Watch where yer goin'!
[BOY 1]
Ha ha!
I guess this place has
people like Tsume, too.
So what now?
Trying to go through the
front gate would be suicide.
Not that that scares me.
Just seems kind
of pointless, is all.
Why mince words?
You wanna find the back door?
Well, if you insist...
I suppose we could.
[CHAMBERLAIN]
Pardon, Milady...
IIt's come to my
attention that #23's signal
has been detected somewhere
within the city walls.
What does Milady desire us do?
23?
[CHAMBERLAIN]
Yes, Milady.
This would mean
they all returned.
The long awaited
time has finally arrived.
[JAGUARA]
Leave me.
[CHAMBERLAIN]
Yes, Milady.
[JAGUARA]
The last wolf...
Hidden by the blinding
light of the moon...
[JAGUARA laughing]
What will he
be like, I wonder...?
This wolf that will
lead me to Paradise...
[TOBOE]
Come on, wait up! Hige!
And just up ahead
there's a little elevator...
And past that...
[TOBOE]
I don't believe it...
This oughta take us
all the way up.
Hey...
Shouldn't we be
heading back by now?
Relax. We'll be fine.
Let's just see how far
we can go' kay?
[TOBOE]
Wow, Hige... how did you know?
You've been here before, right?
[HIGE]
Nope.
But when your instincts
are as sharp as mine are,
you get a feel for things.
I don't like this place...
[QUENT]
Humph.
What can I getcha?
[QUENT] Vodka. And fill
this up for me, will ya?
[SOLDIER B]
So we finally mopped up
what was left of
Orkham's troops, huh?
[SOLDIER C]
What a miserable way to go.
Well, that means the world
belongs to Lady Jaguara now.
[SOLDIER B]
Speakin' o'which,
what's with the snazzy dresser
that was brought in?
[SOLDIER A]
Oh...
you mean that dandy we captured
with the Flower Maiden?
Yeah, Mr. Fancy
Pants keeps claimin'
he's some kind of detective.
I always knew detectives
belonged in the dungeon.
[SOLDIERS laughing]
[BARTENDER]
Excuse me, Sir...
...but something tells me
you're new to this city.
So where are you from?
From the ends of the earth.
I came here lookin' for wolves.
[SOLDIERS laughing]
The old guy says
he's a wolf hunter!
[SOLDIER C] Too bad for him
there're no bounties
to be had around here.
At least not anymore.
[SOLDIERS laughing]
I ain't here for that.
Besides, what difference
would a bounty make?
Sorry about that, old man.
We didn't mean to laugh
at you, it's just that...
It looks like you
got here a little late.
There aren't any wolves.
My men and I have already
killed almost all of them.
We just got a
"mission complete" notification.
It was handed down
from Lady Jaguara herself.
Maybe you don't realize
who you've been talking to.
We're Special Ops: Anti-wolf.
[SOLDIER A] Feel free
to look for 'em if you want,
but trust me, pal,
you're not gonna find any.
[SOLDIERS laughing]
Those things aren't
that easy to kill.
There are still
wolves around here.
I know it for a fact.
[SOLDIERS laughing]
Hey...
How come there isn't
any scent in this place?
[HIGE]
Who knows.
Maybe that Jaguara
lady's a clean freak.
[TOBOE]
Wait up, would ya?
What's the matter?
[HIGE]
Every time I try to think,
my head starts pounding.
Probably not used
to the strain, is all.
Hige, please.
Tell me what's wrong.
Nothin's wrong, okay?
[TOBOE] C'mon, you've been
acting weird since we got here.
Get off my back, will ya?!
Hige!
[HIGE yells]
Hige?
[yelling continues]
Hige!
[TOBOE]
[door opens]
[SHOPKEEP]
Thief!
[BOY 1]
Ha ha!
Remind you of anyone?
Even this city has
people like the old you.
Yeah. Looks that way.
But it's guys like that
who know the back alleys
better than anyone.
What the hell
do you want?!
[TSUME]
I wanna talk.
[BOY 1]
Wha--?
Keep walkin', pal.
I'm not in the mood
for handouts.
Go get your own food!
I just wanna ask
you a question.
Look...
I'm tired and hungry
so leave me alone.
What's the deal?
Hey, if you guys wanna fight,
it's fine by me.
[crash]
[gun clicks]
Uh... You're the man!
[BOY 1]
Huh?
All right, I give.
You guys are too tough
to argue with.
So, where are you from, anyway?
[TSUME]
Oh, here and there.
I know the feeling.
Me and "Verbal" here
have been wanderin'
from dome to dome ever
since the fat hit the fire.
They said this one was
the best of the lot
so we decided to check it out.
I can't say that
I agree with them.
Can you?
[BOY 1] So... You got
a question? Fire away.
[TSUME] We're trying
to get into the keep.
Is there a way to do it
without getting spotted?
[BOY 1]
Huh?
Are you guys nuts?
You don't mean Lady
Jaguara's keep, do ya?
[TSUME]
Uh huh.
Oh, forget it!
I know you're strong and all,
but not even the two of you
could get in there.
Why the hell would
you even wanna do it
in the first place?
They stole a woman from us.
And you wanna steal her
back from that Noble?!
You must really
think I'm a sucker.
We're serious.
But that's suicide!
You can't mess around
with a Noble!
Especially Lady Jaguara.
Word on the street is
she's some kinda witch
who casts all these
whacked out spells.
[KIBA] We don't care
who or what she is.
We came all this way
to save Cheza...
and there's nothing
they can do to stop us.
Oh man.
You're guys are askin' for
a whole mess of trouble,
ya know that?
But hey, if that's what ya want,
it's not like I give a crap.
We can show you the way in,
but that's all.
That'll be enough.
Once we're in, I'm sure we
can handle the rest of it.
Damn, you're cool.
He's the man.
What is this?
Some kind of shakedown?
You bitches tricked me!
[CHER] Do you want
to get slapped again?
All right, enough already!
Fine! You can have them!
Here. Now get lost.
If you'd done this
in the first place,
you never would have
gotten yourself hurt.
Beautiful flowers
always have thorns.
You would do well
to remember that.
[BOY 1]
This is it.
No one's ever followed it all
the way to the end before,
but the cables around here
definitely run
underneath the keep.
With any luck,
they should get you in.
[TSUME]
Right.
[BOY 1] Some guy told me
that these things
are supposed to carry energy
into the city or somethin'.
Do you feel that?
Yeah.
It's the complete opposite
of basking in the moonlight.
It feels like my strength's
being sucked out.
And somethin' tells me it's only
gonna get worse up ahead.
I know.
Listen...
Are you really goin' in there?
Yeah.
Thanks for the help, guys.
You know, Tsume...
The others might
be waiting for us.
[TSUME]
Do you wanna turn back?
Then let's keep going.
Knowing Hige, I'm sure
he'll catch up with us
sooner or later.
We just need to
have a little faith.
Good luck, wolves.
You can do it.
[BOY 1]
Huh?
Damn it!
What the hell's
wrong with me?
Why am I...?
[HIGE yelling]
[HIGE yells]
[SOLDIER D]
#23, huh?
[SOLDIER E] Doesn't look like
any others are with him.
Why did they spare me?
I don't get it...
[HIGE groaning]
My head...
What's going on?
[HIGE]
Damn, my head hurts!
At times like this,
a little temple rub
from a cute girl would
fix me up in a flash.
Oh well...
There's no sense in dreaming.
Guess I'll have to try
some pickled plums.