[WOLF] They say there's no
such place... as Paradise.
Even if you search to
the ends of the earth,
there's nothing there.
No matter how far you walk,
it's always the same road.
It just goes on and on.
[WOLF] But in spite of that,
why am I so driven to find it?
[WOLF]
A voice calls to me. It says:
"Search for Paradise."
Let's go.
Hurry up!
Dumbass!
[clatter]
[GEHL]
Tsume!
[REBELS cheering]
[SEDO]
That's a Noble's ship.
I hate that sound.
[QUENT]
Vodka.
I'll tell you this lousy
city isn't fit for a dog,
much less a man.
Never thought it'd be
so cold inside a dome.
Well I don't know where
you're from, mister,
but I doubt there's anywhere
fit to live these days.
Always helps to have a friend
when you're crossin'
the mountains.
Never know what
you might run into.
Like bears... or wolves.
[BARTENDER]
Wolves?
Now there's something I haven't
heard about in a long time.
Not since my grandpa was alive.
He always used to tell me
when the world finally
comes to an end,
Paradise will appear
on the Earth.
But the trouble
is that only wolves
would know where to find it.
Who knows. Maybe the world
is coming to an end right now.
[thunk]
Wolves are only
servants of Death!
Don't you believe all
that pagan garbage.
Relax, old man.
Wolves have been
extinct for 200 years.
It's just kids' fairy tales.
[QUENT]
The thing about fairy tales is
there's always
some truth in 'em.
What? What is it, Blue?
Did you see one?
[CHEN]
Hey, Tsume!
Where's the fire?
Can't we slow down a little?
There's nobody's following us.
I know...
Haven't we gotten
enough already?
I mean, there's
plenty to go around.
The provisions for the Nobles
are gonna be passing through
the checkpoint tomorrow.
[ALL]
Huh?
We're gonna hit 'em again?
[TSUME] Chen, Sedo, you're
in the advance squad.
Why doesn't that surprise me?
Yeah, but we messed it
up bad there last week.
Security's gonna be
even tighter now.
We lost two of us
today as it is.
[TSUME]
Ghel, you're on standby.
Anyone who isn't willing
to fight should get out now.
[REBELS whispering]
[TSUME]
What is it?
It's a dog, but I don't
think it's gonna make it.
[gasps]
[CHEN]
Maybe it's worth something.
[SEDO]
Maybe we can eat it.
[REBEL A] I've never seen a dog
this big. The suckers huge!
[TSUME]
That is not a dog.
[REBELS]
Huh?
[TSUME]
Pull it out.
Okay...
[yelps]
[whimpering]
How interesting.
That was quite a stunt.
[WOLF] I was protecting
myself. That's all.
[TSUME]
Don't be so quick to kill.
[WOLF]
What's wrong with killing?
[TSUME] I don't know what
mountain you came down from,
but you're in the city now.
There are rules.
[WOLF]
Rules?
Is running around this
city with a pack of idiots
one of the rules?
I'm only using 'em.
[WOLF] Your rules stink
like this city.
What's the point of living if it
means throwing away your pride?
You gotta a big mouth
for someone half dead.
[BOTH gasp]
[WOLVES barking]
[gasps]
[yelling]
Are you okay, Tsume?
Hey, you're bleeding...
Don't touch me!
[TSUME]
And stay outta my business.
I wanted to thank you.
You saved my life back there.
I always thought
maybe you didn't care
if one of your
friends got killed.
I guess I thought, maybe I'd
never be one of your friends.
[TSUME]
We're not friends.
It's just... I'm not
like you people.
I've never seen this expression
on her face before.
Has the solution been altered?
No. It's the same as always.
Do you think she's awakened?
[CHER] According to the data
we found, the first thing
Cheza's showed a response
to was blood, wasn't it?
[FEMALE SCIENTIST]
Wolf's blood, you mean.
[CHER] Yes... The smell
of wolf's blood.
[MALE SCIENTIST] But, what
evidence is there that...?
[CHER]
None.
Many things exist that can't be
explained by scientific proof
simply due to a
lack of evidence.
Cheza herself is the crowning
achievement of an alchemy
that can not be proved.
The Flower Maiden and the wolves
are being drawn to one another.
Like an ancient
scholar's fairy tale.
[siren wailing]
[HUBB]
Quent Yaiden.
So tell me, what brings
the sheriff of Kyrios
to our humble city?
That's some heavy artillery
you've got, there.
But I doubt you came all
this way for the hunting.
[QUENT]
What did you do with it?
Where's the animal I put down?
[HUBB]
Dead, apparently.
Huh?
[HUBB] The carcass will
be disposed of here.
That's impossible!
There's not a chance in
hell that thing is dead.
I have to see it
with my own eyes.
Don't you get it? It's a wolf!
You think it's a wolf?
[QUENT] It may look like a dog,
but it's not. It's a wolf!
You don't honestly believe
that we wiped those things
from the face of the
planet, do you, detective?
The last appearance of a
wolf was over 200 years ago.
Just, how do you propose
they survived all this time?
The mountains and forests
have been stripped bare.
There's nowhere on earth
they could live or hide.
They're all around us!
They've just put us all
under some kind of spell!
The wolves exist and we
have to destroy them all.
[HUBB]
I figured this sort of thing
might be under
your jurisdiction.
[CHER]
So it's alive?
Just barely. But it's
only a matter of time.
That sounds like the two of us.
We're not over yet.
All we have to do
is keep trying.
I'm not so sure.
What are you doing?
What department are you with?
[HIGE]
Oh, uh, sorry.
I was lookin' for
cleaning supplies.
I guess I must've got lost.
[HUBB]
The cleaning crew, huh?
Just go out that door.
Supplies are on the right.
[HIGE]
Oh, are they? Thanks.
So, do you think
it's really a wolf?
I don't know.
I've never seen
a real one before.
But if it is a wolf,
it may be what's causing this
sudden reaction in Cheza.
[HUBB]
Oh, please. Not Cheza again.
What's that mean?
It's because of her
you and I broke up.
Stop acting like an idiot, Hubb,
and bring this up to the lab.
I'll have someone do it later.
Dogs and I don't get
along all that well.
I'm kind of allergic to them.
[groans]
This is the reason you
and I would never work.
I dunno, maybe it is
just a matter of time.
I'm coming with you guys.
I wanna fight.
I can help you.
Just tell me what to do.
Man, you really screwed up.
I mean, I've seen one
of us get caught before,
but never this badly.
[WOLF] I can get out of here
whenever I feel like it.
Uh-huh. So then why
are you in there?
[WOLF] I just needed a place
to rest for a while. That's all.
[chuckles]
I'm Hige, it's
nice to meet 'cha.
[WOLF]
So, why are you here, anyway?
No reason.
It smelled like something
interesting was gonna happen
and I just followed
my nose, you know?
Besides, I got
nowhere else to go.
[WOLF]
That's not your true form.
Why do you hide yourself?
[HIGE] So I don't
end up where you are.
These people are
terrified of us.
So, you know, if
we look like them,
they pretty much leave us alone.
[WOLF]
You're living a lie
just so you can die a
miserable death in this city?
Gotta do what you can
to survive, right?
Keep looking like that,
you'll be back here in no time.
It draws too much attention.
[WOLF] Have you given up
your pride as a wolf?
[HIGE]
Hm?
You're a strange one, all right.
But having pride doesn't count
for much if you're dead, y'know?
[alarm blaring]
[gasps]
Tsume!
[screaming]
[DISPATCH RADIO]
All units,
we have a disturbance
at checkpoint 12.
One deceased male, late teens.
Sir! That big dog!
It disappeared!
[HUBB]
What?
[HUBB] It's gone. Do you
think someone stole it?
Could be. Or maybe it
escaped on it's own.
[HIGE] Your wounds.
Have they healed?
[WOLF] Yeah. After all,
it's a full moon tonight.
[HIGE] So, why'd you come to
this crummy town, anyway?
[WOLF]
I smelled something.
The scent of Lunar Flower.
It's here in this city.
[HIGE]
Yeah, I know.
My nose can tell
when a dog's takin' a dump
ten kilometers away.
Yeah? That must really stink.
[chuckles]
Sure does.
[WOLF]
So why did you escape with me?
Oh, I dunno. I just
felt like it, I guess.
Besides, you seem
kinda interesting.
So what's next?
Where're ya headed?
To Paradise.
There isn't any
moonlight in this place.
Paradise, huh?
That sounds like fun.
My name is... Kiba.
[BOY] I met the cutest girl by
that garbage dump in the alley.
She gave me food
and everything!
She's so nice. Really nice.
Oh wait... you don't
know me yet, do ya?
Just watch the next
episode. You'll see.