[NEIGE]
Lord Darcia.
A wolf has appeared in
the domed city to the north.
They have not been seen
since passing into
legend 200 years ago.
[DARCIA]
Yes. You were but a child then.
[DARCIA] The Flower Maiden.
Has she awoken?
[NEIGE]
So it would seem.
[DARCIA]
Hamona.
Very soon, you will
awaken as well, my love...
[CHER]
Anything on the Kirlian?
[FEMALE SCIENTIST]
Spectral radiation unchanged.
[CHER]
Any response to the tests?
[FEMALE SCIENTIST]
None. Just as we suspected.
So she's been awake
this whole time.
Yes. Although she appears
to be rather calm now.
The data indicates that she's
still in a fairly excited state.
[MALE SCIENTIST]
Doctor Degre? You've got a call.
[CHER]
Who is it?
[MALE SCIENTIST]
It's your husband.
Uh... I mean your ex-husband.
[clears throat]
Uh...
Detective Lebowski
is on line one.
Yes, what is it?
C'mon, Cher,
does it really matter what
title they call me by?
[CHER]
Just tell me what you want.
[sighs]
[HUBB] There's something
I need you to see.
So, what did you catch
this time, an elephant?
Sorry, humans aren't
really my specialty.
[HUBB] He was one of the kids
involved in the warehouse theft.
He fell from the roof
while trying to escape.
Are these tooth
marks from a dog?
The wounds are still pretty
fresh. What do ya think?
Are you trying to tell me
the dog that escaped did this?
[HUBB]
I don't know.
I should've take molds of its
teeth when I had the chance.
I wonder why it
hasn't been found yet.
With a dog that big running
wild around the city,
you'd think someone
would've reported it.
Maybe they are
trying to deceive us.
[CHER]
Huh?
[HUBB]
No. Forget it. It's impossible.
Oh, Hubb.
Am I down here just because
you wanted to see me?
[HUBB]
Uh.
Maybe just a little.
You never change, do you?
[footsteps]
[DOG whines]
Here. Try some of these.
They taste better.
Come on, you can have 'em.
You are hungry, aren't you?
[CROW caws]
Don't be afraid.
They're not poisoned
or anything.
See, it's fine.
Where'd you come
from little fella?
If you wander around
here too long,
the dog catchers'll
get you for sure.
Ya sure are warm,
aren't ya, boy?
[MAN]
Leara!
[LEARA]
Bye, now.
No, stay.
Sorry, boy, but even
if you followed me home,
I couldn't keep you.
Well that's funny, it's almost
like you can understand me.
I'm sorry.
[COP B]
Hold 'im!
[BOY A] Lemme go, dammit!
I didn't do anything!
[HOUSEWIFE]
Did you hear?
Someone saw a wolf in town.
Can you believe it?
What is this world coming to?
You don't suppose it was
just a big dog, do you?
[HOUSEWIFE]
From what I heard,
no one's ever seen
a dog that big before.
Oh, these are troubled times.
[HIGE] See? What'd I
tell ya, nobody notices us.
This is awful.
That's the best you
can get around here.
If I see a deer loping by,
I'll be sure to catch it for ya.
The Nobles are at it again.
Seems like they pick up
one idiot after another.
[KIBA] Where do the troops take
them once they're caught?
Well, the same place
they took you, I guess.
That's perfect.
[HIGE]
Huh?
I'll blend in and sneak inside.
What?
But we had to fool them
just to get outta there.
That hotdog fried your brain.
I'm going back in.
Now wait a second. What the
hell happened to Paradise?
Look, the scent is coming from
somewhere inside that building.
And as far as we can tell, the
only way in is to get captured.
You know what's
there, don't you?
What they're hiding
behind those walls?
The beacon that will
lead us to Paradise.
Well, forget it. You'll
never get close to Cheza.
[KIBA]
Cheza?
[HIGE] The Flower Maiden that
was created from Lunar Flowers.
That's what they say, anyway.
Listen, it's useless. They
got that place locked down.
Even I couldn't get
as far as the lab.
So then why did you
try to sneak in there?
For a little
excitement, I guess.
[KIBA] Hige, don't you
believe in Paradise, too?
I'm not goin'. No way.
[KIBA]
All right. See ya around.
Hey, Kiba!
Try to give a guy advice
and what does it get ya?
See if I care.
[CHEN] They say the
Noble's have put a bounty
on every gang in the city.
[TSUME]
Is that so?
Yeah, they've already
started to round people up.
And our stuff's been
kinda high profile lately.
We figure we're next.
Maybe it's time
we should move on.
There's a freight train
pullin' outta town at midnight.
--We can sneak on.
--[TSUME] Our next raid
[TSUME]
is gonna be tonight.
Make the usual preparations.
[CHEN] Why, so you can
just sit back and watch?
Gehl's dead because
of you. You let 'im die.
Sorry, pal, but I ain't workin'
with you anymore.
I wouldn't wanna slow
you down, now would I?
[TSUME]
Suit yourself.
We'll meet up at midnight.
Get the word out.
[CHER] We analyzed the dog
hairs from inside the cage
and they don't match the ones
that were found on the corpse.
There's also a third set
of hairs yet unidentified.
A third set?
As far as we can tell,
there were two types of
hair around the cage.
What the hell is going on?
There isnt' anywhere
for them to hide.
You okay? You're not
acting like yourself.
No offence, but I thought
you didn't like dogs.
And to be honest,
you're starting to
sound a little obsessed.
I am not obsessed,
Cher. Don't worry.
I'm probably just looking for
another excuse to see you.
[phone clicks]
It may be time to
track down that guy.
Listen up, Blue. I know
you can understand me.
You can't let them get away.
Wolves are evil. They'll kill
ya if they get the chance.
Right now they're
lying low somewhere,
breathing their foul,
demon's breath.
Uh. Uh!
Thanks a lot... for before.
[LEARA]
Huh?
For the sausages.
Uh, remember back in the alley?
Well, that was my dog
you gave them to.
That beautiful dog
belongs to you?
That beautiful--
Uh, yeah! Yeah, he's mine!
But how'd you know about it?
Um, I... I heard it from
the lady at the store.
What's a name anyway?
A name?
[chuckles]
The name is Toboe.
Toboe?
[chuckles] What a weird name.
You think so?
Yeah, I guess it is.
My name is Leara.
What's yours?
I just said. It's Toboe.
I thought that was
your dog's name.
Uh... Well we're a lot alike.
So I decided to name
him after myself.
You're pretty
weird all right.
[chuckling]
[TOBOE chuckling]
[TOBOE gasps]
Your another one.
Just like me.
Move it, kid.
Ya find somethin'?
[QUENT]
A boy?
No.
You're not a boy...
Jump!
Hurry up!
Uh, I was getting ready to!
That was them.
I finally found 'em.
Who the heck was that?
And what's up with his dog?
I've no idea.
Hey, you're Tsume, right?
This is a first for me.
I've never met a wolf.
I mean, other than myself.
I heard rumors about you
from the crows though.
Uh, they said you make
friends with humans
and run wild with them.
[TOBOE chuckles]
Ya heard wrong.
I don't have friends.
I'm Toboe. Thanks for
the help back there.
Y'know what? I've been living
with human's my whole life--
[TSUME]
Just get lost, will ya?
I'm getting pissed off.
And that only happens
when I'm around idiots.
[TOBOE]
But... can't I come with you?
[TSUME]
No. You can't.
Yo.
Hige.
What in the world
are you doin' in here?
C'mon, we're friends
now, aren't we?
Comin' from you that
sounds kinda fishy.
[BIRD caws]
Leara!
Here. It's your bird.
[TOBOE]
Hey. Wake up.
Leara.
He's dead.
My bird's dead.
But I...
I didn't mean to
kill him, I swear.
I knew it was yours
and I just wanted to...
I didn't think it would die...
[TOBOE crying, snarling]
[howling]
I never meant to
kill anything...
[TOBOE]
Granny, she...
I was all alone at the
entrance to the dome...
...and she was so nice to me.
She said I was so little
my eyes had barely opened.
She gave these to me, and
we lived together ever since.
You mean she kept you as a pet.
That human tamed you.
You were nothing more
than an obedient dog.
[TOBOE]
I wasn't!
I... I only...
I wanted to protect her,
but... she still...
[TSUME]
She still threw you out?
[TOBOE]
She still died.
She died...
[TOBOE]
I... let her die.
[footsteps]
Well, look who it is.
Detective Dandy.
[HUBB] I need to ask
you some questions.
[QUENT] And there's something
that you need to see.
[TSUME]
Sedo.
No one is gonna come.
[TSUME]
Then why are you here?
I'm leaving after this.
Tsume. You're just too
different from the rest of us.
[gasps]
[KIBA]
Did you feel that?
Feel what?
[KIBA] This isn't right.
Something's gonna happen.
[HIGE sniffing]
I don't smell anything.
Except for mildew.
It's getting closer.
So, you wanna break out of here?
[KIBA]
Yeah.
[MALE SCIENTIST B]
Doctor? Doctor Degre?
[CHER] Oh, is it that late
already? Did something happen?
[MALE SCIENTIST B]
No, ma'am.
There's been no change
for a while now,
so I thought you might
wanna call it a night.
I'm too pretty to
look like this.
What the hell?
Everything's fine.
The lab's power supply is
independent from the main grid.
[DARCIA]
Yes, I know.
[DARCIA] Cheza... is not vital
to you. Is that correct?
Who are you?
[DARCIA]
Everyone is resting now.
You look exhausted as well.
[DARCIA] So tired.
You should rest a while.
[DARCIA]
It's been a long time, Cheza.
[DARCIA] You can sense
my presence, can't you?
Though your eyes do not see me.
[DARCIA]
There is nothing to fear.
You are awake, now, at last.
[DARCIA] We can finally
set out on our journey.
[HIGE]
This way.
[QUENT]
There are times in a man's life
when he's gotta take a journey.
Just like there are times
when he gotta take a drink.
Ah...
There's nothin' like warm
vodka on a cold night.