Kiba!
[HIGE]
Damn it, will you wait up?!
[panting]
C'mon You're goin' too fast.
Let's take a break.
We don't have time for that.
Would you use your
head for once!
We've got a girl and
a little kid with us.
[BLUE]
I can hear you, y'know.
Don't worry about me.
I can keep up.
Yeah, me, too!
You realize he's the one who
wants to rest, don't you?
I do not! I just...
But you've gotta admit,
he does have a point.
At this rate, none
of us will make it.
We can take shelter in those
rocks till the storm clears.
That settles it, then.
Can you guys hang
in a little longer?
[BLUE] Just worry about
yourself, all right?
[HIGE]
Yes ma'am. Sorry.
Let's go.
The sun'll be up soon.
We should rest here until then.
What do you say, Kiba?
I mean, the storm will blow
itself out by morning.
[KIBA]
It already has.
[BOTH gasp]
Come on. It'll be fine.
Well, none of us will be fine!
Do what you want, I'm leaving.
[BLUE]
Look, I can handle it.
[TOBOE]
Yeah. Let's get going.
[HIGE]
No!
I'm not goin' anywhere
till morning.
I understand.
Kiba!
Let him go.
[TOBOE]
But, why...
Right now, the only thing
he can see is Cheza.
It doesn't make any difference
whether we're with him or not.
We'll follow him once
the storm blows over.
For now, just get some rest
and don't worry about it.
Hige. Y'sure about this?
[HIGE exhales]
He obsesses too much.
What can ya do?
[snoring]
So, I take it...
you didn't like the
scarf that much, huh?
It's really too bad, I
thought it suited you.
Uh. I guess not.
[laughing]
You lunkhead.
[CHER]
Cheza is...
a girl made from lunar flowers
by utilizing an ancient alchemy.
It was Lord Darcia the
First who created her.
[CHER]
She was stolen by Lord Orkham
and brought to the
lab for us to study,
hoping that we could awaken her,
and open the gates of Paradise.
[HUBB]
Paradise...?
[CHER] It's a world where
wolves reign supreme.
They're drawn to
the Lunar Flower
because it's the one
thing that can guide
the world's remaining
wolves to Paradise.
Tell me, Cher.
Did you know about all of this
from the very beginning?
Then who told you?!
Wait a minute.
You mean, at the keep
we're headed towards...?
[QUENT]
A world full of wolves, huh?
If that's what you
call Paradise,
I'll take my chances in
Hell any day of the week.
[HUBB]
Quent, you were awake?
[QUENT] Hey, what can I say,
it's too cold to stay drunk.
The Book of the Moon.
It isn't just a fairy
tale, you know.
[QUENT]
Maybe.
But even if you're right,
there's nothing we humans can
do about it now, is there.
I'll never be able to
forgive the wolves.
Not after what they did.
Even if they are the "supreme
rulers" of this rotten world,
I'm gonna eradicate
every one of them.
My Lord Darcia. Inside
the keep, there's...
[DARCIA]
A wolf?
Yes.
[DARCIA] My love, now
that I have lost you,
Paradise holds no meaning
for me. And yet...
[DARCIA whimpers]
[DARCIA]
This wolf's eye throbs...
Why?
What is this feeling that
threatens to overwhelm me?
My beloved Hamona.
Tell me. What should I...
He is here.
So, this is the keep of Darcia.
Place looks like it
should be haunted.
By what...?
By the ghosts of all
the cursed Nobles.
C'mon, don't say
stuff like that.
But still,
are you sure that girl
is inside of there?
[sniffs] The scent is faint,
but it's definitely
a Lunar Flower.
[TSUME]
He's got visitors.
[gasps]
Hey, hold on!
Pops is here.
[HIGE] Blue, what is it?
What's gotten into you?
[TOBOE]
Come on!
[HUBB]
Who are the Nobles, anyway?
[CHER] There was extensive
literature dealing
with the Nobility,
but most of it was lost with
the decline of civilization.
Yet, there are some
things we do know.
They say that long before the
world became as it is now,
the Nobles extolled the
virtues of this culture.
By using an amazing
form of alchemy,
they blazed a path to the stars
and opened the doors
to space and time.
But in an instant, all
of it simply vanished.
No one really knows
what happened then,
but many people disappeared.
The development and
execution of their alchemy
came to be a secret known
only to the remaining Nobles
that was never to be
passed on to the people.
All of that happened
almost 200 years ago.
And now what remains of this
world is slowly fading away.
Along with the blood red moon.
He is here.
[gasps]
Cheza!
Kiba!
Why the hell are you
in such a rush?
It's Pops. I know he's here.
But do you really
wanna see him?
That Pops guy?
No. It might be
better if I didn't.
But maybe the reason
he's out here...
is to find you.
[TSUME]
So... What if he is?
Are you gonna go back to
being that human's dog?
Hey, lay off!
Yeah, Tsume, be quiet!
You don't know what it's like.
Guess I don't.
Unlike the two of you, I've
never had the "pleasure"
of being kept as a pet.
Now, now. Let's find
Kiba and Cheza.
We can fight later.
The flower scent's
comin' from over there.
The worship of wolves, huh?
But it's not just a
simple animal cult.
It's deeper than that.
I think the vision of this
world has split somehow.
There's one we humans can see
and one we must've lost
sight of at some point.
I'm fairly certain the
animals are aware of that.
Including the wolves?
[sneezes]
What the hell
brought that on?
[HUBB] I have a terrible
allergy to dogs.
[sneezes]
That a fact?
Then they must be over this way.
Those allergies sure
do come in handy.
[HUBB]
Glad I could help.
Kiba!
[gasps]
[CHEZA gasping, screams]
Cheza!
[DARCIA growls]
[DARCIA] So, wolf.
Have you come for revenge?
[KIBA]
You... will not... hurt Cheza!
Cheza. She is a being
that we created,
the mere embodiment
of a Lunar Flower.
Why is it that your desire
for her so desperate?
[KIBA] I don't know
who you Nobles are,
or what you're tryin' to do.
And to be honest,
I don't really care.
Cheza's all that matters.
She'sgonna show us
the way to Paradise.
You damn wolf...
All of this first began
with your wretched breed.
[HUBB]
What is it?
Hey!
[DARCIA]
It's because of you...
You and your kind stole
everything from me.
And in return you
gave me a curse.
And grief. And suffering.
And my eye
transformed into
one such as yours.
The price I paid for being
cursed by Paradise.
And now...
the only thing that
surrounds me is despair.
[KIBA]
Don't!
What is it, what do you want?!
[DARCIA]
Have you found it?
Have you found Paradise?
[KIBA]
We will. No matter what!
[DARCIA] And what do you
expect to find there?
[KIBA]
A future.
[DARCIA]
A future...?
[KIBA]
Not hope...
or despair.
Just a future. Nothin' more.
I no longer have any need...
for a... future.
--[gunshot]
--[ALL gasp]
It's over, wolf.
No, don't!!
[gasps]
B-Blue...
Kiba!
[NEIGE gasps]
[NEIGE]
My Lord Darcia!
[KIBA]
Cheza!
[TSUME]
Kiba!
Cheza!
Blue, no!
[CHER]
Cheza.
[HUBB]
We have to hurry.
How could you...?
Why, Blue?
[HUBB]
Quent!
[QUENT]
Blue!
Jaguara!
[BLUE growling]
[BLUE]
That way!
[CHER gasps]
Did that wolf just
say something?
[CHER]
Uh.
[HIGE]
Kiba!
[TSUME]
What are you doing?!
Kiba!
[gasps]
[BOTH gasp]
Kiba!
[TOBOE]
[howling]
[NEIGE] A human life
is an ephemeral thing.
It is always wise to look back
on one's past from time to time.
But perhaps my life is a trifle
too long to dwell upon.
And so, I bid you adieu.