[TSUME]
I can't remember anymore
how long it's been since
I first found my way here.
Or even why the hell
I decided to come.
The stench of this city only
adds to the pervading filth.
The cold wind that creeps in
through the cracks in the dome
makes it way into every
damn inch of this place.
Scavenging rats
feeding off the trash.
Greedy, gossiping crows.
Humans with exhausted faces.
Residents perfectly suited
to life in this city.
[BOY A]
Ah! What the hell?!
Lemme go, I didn't...
[TSUME]
And me?
Hmph.
What else... I was starving.
Let's go.
Hurry up!
[GEHL yelps]
[REBEL A]
Dumbass!
[REBEL A grunting]
[GEHL whimpers]
[GEHL]
TSUME!
[ALL cheering]
[TSUME] There's a risk that
comes with almost everything,
but if you're strong enough,
you can always get food.
Survival of the fittest.
It's the one rule that applies
no matter where you go.
This city isn't really so bad.
I found a place where
I truly belonged.
Everything was fine,
and then he showed up.
[TSUME]
What is it?
[REBEL B]
It's a dog.
I don't think it's
gonna make it.
[gasps]
[CROWD murmurs]
[CHEN]
Maybe it's worth something.
[SEDO]
Maybe we can eat it!
[REBEL B] I've never seen a dog
this big. Th'suckers huge!
[TSUME]
That is not a dog.
[ALL]
Huh?
[TSUME]
Pull it out.
[BOTH]
Mm. Uh...
Okay
[REBEL B groaning]
[REBEL C screams]
[GEHL whimpers]
How interesting.
That was quite a stunt.
[KIBA]
I was protecting myself.
That's all.
[TSUME]
Don't be so quick to kill.
[KIBA]
What's wrong with killing?
[TSUME] I don't know what
mountain you came down from,
but you're in the city
now. There are rules.
[KIBA]
Rules?!
Is running around this city
with a pack of idiots
one of the rules?
I'm only using 'em.
[KIBA]
Your rules stink like this city
What's the point of living if it
means throwin' away your pride?
You gotta big mouth
for someone half dead!
[gasps]
[TSUME grunts]
[GEHL]
Are you okay, Tsume?
Hey, you're bleeding.
Don't touch me!
[GEHL gasping]
[TSUME]
And stay out of my business.
I wanted to thank you.
You saved my life back there.
I always thought
maybe you didn't care
if one of your
friends got killed.
I guess,
I thought maybe I'd never
be one of your friends.
[TSUME]
We're not friends.
[GEHL]
Huh?
It's just, I'm not
like you people.
[panting]
[CHEN]
Hey, Tsume!
Where's the fire?
Can't we slow down a little,
there's nobody's followin' us.
[TSUME]
I know.
[SEDO] Haven't we
gotten enough already?
I mean, there's plenty
to go around.
The provisions for the Nobles
are gonna be passing through
the checkpoint tomorrow.
[ALL]
Huh?
We're gonna hit 'em again?
[TSUME] Chen, Sedo,
you're in the advance squad.
Why doesn't that surprise me?
Yeah, but we messed it
up bad there last week.
Security's gonna be
even tighter now.
We lost two of us
today as it is.
[TSUME]
Gehl, you'll be on standby.
[gasps]
Anyone who isn't willing to
fight should get out now.
[TSUME] In the end,
it's a human city.
It's much too cramped
for a wolf to live in.
Hmph. I guess I knew
that from the beginning.
I could try and run
from it all I wanted,
but this burning
feeling in my gut
would never disappear.
I'm coming with you
guys. I wanna fight.
I can help you. Just
tell me what to do.
[GEHL gasping]
Tsume!
[gasps]
[screams]
[CHEN] They say the Noble's
have put a bounty
on every gang in the city.
[TSUME]
Is that so?
[SEDO] Yeah, they've already
started to round people up.
And our stuff's been kinda
high profile lately.
Maybe it's time
we should move on.
There's a freight train pullin'
outta town at midnight.
We can sneak on--
[TSUME] Our next raid
is gonna be tonight.
Make the usual
preparations.
[CHEN] Why,' so you can
just sit back and watch?
Gehl's dead because of you.
You let 'im die.
Sorry pal, but I ain't
workin' with you anymore.
I wouldn't want to slow
you down, now would I?
[TSUME]
Suit yourself.
[HOUSEWIFE] Did you hear?
Someone saw a wolf in town.
Can you believe it?
[FEMALE EMPLOYEE]
What is this world coming to?
You don't suppose...
it was just a big dog, do you?
[HOUSEWIFE]
From what I heard,
no one's ever seen a
dog that big before.
Oh, these are troubled times.
[TSUME] No matter where we
go, nothing ever changes.
We may disguise our true form,
but we're still wolves.
I should have known better
than to get mixed up
with a clumsy pup like him.
[QUENT]
A boy?
No...
You're not a boy.
[QUENT gasps]
[TOBOE whimpers]
Jump!
Hurry up!
Uh. I was getting ready to!
Hey, you're Tsume, right?
This is a first for me.
I've never met a wolf.
I mean other than myself.
I heard rumors about you
from the crows, though.
Uh. They said you make
friends with humans
and run wild with
them. Heh, heh.
[TSUME] Ya heard wrong.
I don't have friends.
I'm Toboe. Thanks for
the help back there.
Y'know what?
I've been living with
humans my whole life, too
[TSUME]
Just get lost, will ya?
I'm getting pissed off
and that only happens
when I'm around idiots.
[TSUME gasps]
[TOBOE]
So what are you gonna do now?
Do you have somewhere to go?
[TSUME]
Who knows.
I wonder if I'll ever
see Leara again?
Hey, you think it'd be okay
if I went to visit her?
[TSUME] You saw that look
on her face, didn't you?
[TOBOE] She was just... a
little surprised, that's all.
[TSUME] You can't be serious!
She was pissing in her pants!
[TOBOE]
She was not!
That girl was reekin' of it.
[TOBOE] Why do you have
to lie about everything?!
Why can't you just be honest
with yourself for once!
Fine, whatever!
If you wanna go, then go.
It's not like I care
what happens to ya.
[TOBOE]
So why did you save me, then?
If you really don't care then
you should've just left me
or pretended not
to recognize me.
I mean, I'm not your
friend or anything.
[TSUME] You're right.
You're not my friend.
Yeah, I forgot, you're only
friends with humans.
It's easier that way, isn't it,
'cause no human is ever
gonna be as strong as you.
They'll do whatever
you tell them to.
You don't know what
you're talking about!
You have no idea what it takes
to survive in this city,
how dangerous it is. Nothing!
Go on. Let's see how
well you do on your own.
Beat it!
Being alone doesn't
bother you?
Hey, I'm sorry.
[gasps]
I'm sorry I ever got mixed
up with a kid like you.
[TOBOE]
Uh.
I'm sick of friends.
Who needs 'em.
[OFFICERS gasp]
[DETECTIVE A groans]
[SEDO whimpering]
Tsume!
[yelps]
You sold me out?
They caught us when we tried
to sneak onto the train.
We couldn't just let you
get away scot-free.
[TSUME]
Heh. You damn humans.
Huh?
[OFFICERS panting]
[ALL gasp]
You're pretty good.
[TSUME whimpering]
[TSUME]
Damn it!
[HIGE]
What a crap heap.
Why the hell'd you
bring us here?
Tsume!
[HIGE]
Wha...?
I could smell the blood
from your wound.
[TSUME]
What?
[KIBA] I smelled it all
the way here from the town.
[TSUME] And you're gonna
nurse me back to health?
Well, I don't need your help.
[TOBOE]
Tsume... Look, I...
Um.
We're leaving the city.
I really think you
should come with us.
[TSUME] And just where is this
merry band of yours going?
[KIBA]
To Paradise.
Heh. Y' kiddin' me.
You're goin' with them because
you believe in that crap?
Oh, I don't know, but...
if we stay here we'll have to
spend the rest of our lives
in hiding, or worse!
We just can't live with the
humans anymore and survive.
Look, I hate to interrupt, but a
nasty stink is headed this way.
[TSUME]
We're surrounded.
Let me ask you.
Why did you guys
come to this city?
It was because of the
flower scent, wasn't it?
Well, it's gone now.
There's no reason to stay.
The flower has
nothing to do with it.
I'm here because I belong.
[KIBA] I can see that.
This city is a dump.
I still have a score
to settle with you.
We don't have time for this!
The last time we met you said
something about how your pride
wouldn't allow you
to pass as a human.
Well, you look pretty human
now. Where'd your pride go?
Nowhere. Nothing has changed.
Do you have the slightest idea
of what leaving
the city would mean?
[KIBA]
Yeah.
You'll just die.
Possibly. Everyone's gonna die.
It's a natural part of life.
But if your life has no
purpose you're dead already.
[TOBOE groaning]
[TSUME gasps]
[TOBOE grunting]
[TOBOE]
Thank you.
[TSUME]
Go on. Hurry up.
You're really not
coming with us?
[TOBOE]
Tsume!
What the hell're
you stopping for?
Tsume!
This way!
[HIGE]
Jump already!
I was getting ready
to, all right?!
Move it!
[TOBOE yelps]
[QUENT gasps]
[HUBB]
Hey! Wait a minute!
Tsume, what are you
waiting for, come on, jump!
[KIBA]
Are you scared?
Yeah, you wish.
[TSUME]
Screw this stupid journey.
Paradise can kiss my ass!
I'm just fed up with
this stinking town.
It was time to move on anyway.
[KIBA] I saw them once
before, when I was little.
I was still just a cub.
In the region where I was born
they had blossomed all over.
White flowers that only
bloomed under a full moon.
They were Lunar Flowers.
They were all burned to ashes.
[KIBA]
A fire raged across our land.
It burned all the flowers
in an instant, and all...
all of my friends whose escape
route was cut off were killed.
I was the only
one who survived.
Why me? Why just me?
I don't have a pack anymore.
The only place for me now...
is Paradise.
[TOBOE] There're all kinds
of things in this world.
And you can't really do
much about most if it.
But sometimes just waiting
to see what happens
is what makes the journey
fun, don't ya think?
I wonder whatever
happened to that girl?