[HUBB]
A rumor was going around
that there was a theft at
the House of Lord Orkham's
just a month ago.
Yet, apparently it was never
reported to the police.
[SNAKE CHARMER] What a silly
reason to come here.
The more important question
is why are you shaking?
Am I so scary, little boy?
[HUBB] No. Ya see,
I'm allergic to snakes.
[SNAKE CHARMER chuckles]
[SNAKE CHARMER] I've never
heard that one before.
Come on, you can talk
about work later, right?
Well, the truth is
I always embarrass myself
in situations like this.
Pretty sick of it myself.
Oh. That's the cutest
line I've ever heard.
But never the less,
it's not really customary
for a detective to go digging
around in a Noble's affairs.
What are you after?
I'm looking for someone.
[SNAKE CHARMER]
Your lover?
My ex-wife.
Is that so?
It's been said that the thieves
who got into the castle
were the last survivors
of a fallen Noble family.
The lord of the manor
has his pride, you know?
I think he wants to
catch them himself.
Is that why it wasn't reported?
Perhaps he wanted to keep
whatever was stolen a secret
from the police, ya know?
Thank you.
A glass of whatever'll
warm me up.
[BARTENDER]
Yes, sir.
I'd like a chilled
sherry, please.
[BARTENDER]
Yes, ma'am.
[BOTH]
Hit me again.
Looks like ya still got
a fair amount of tourists
around this place.
All the uninvited
ones, anyway.
So what do they
come here to see?
That old castle on
the mountaintop?
That place is nothing
but ruins now.
And besides, you can't
get anywhere near it.
Oh?
There're wolves up there.
[QUENT]
What?
[PATRONS laughing]
Give me another.
[BARTENDER] Don't you
think you've had enough?
I guess.
[growling]
Cheza?
We have a friend, even here.
It is all right.
You do not know what
you are. You never did.
Is that not right?
There is some wolf
inside of you, too.
[CHEZA] You were alone your
whole life, were you not?
[KIBA]
Cheza!
[RETRIEVAL LEADER]
No doubt about it, sir.
We've pinpointed
the target's location.
Good. Continue to
keep a trace on them.
Should we hit 'em
all at once, sir?
No, make sure the
town's surrounded first.
After you've cut off
all their escape routes,
I want you to move your men
in and capture the target.
Yes, sir!
What about the woman?
You can ignore her. At
this point she's useless.
This should be a
perfect place to hide.
Once we catch wind
of what they're up to,
we'll come right back.
Cheza, you stay here with Toboe.
Leave it to me!
Don't be too long, okay?!
[TOBOE]
I like this.
The idea of friends
waiting for other friends,
it's really a nice feeling.
If you know what I mean.
What is it?
This one is stuffed.
And you?
Um... Sure.
[RETRIEVAL LEADER]
This way! Get 'em!
Hasu, let's meet up in town!
[HASU]
Right!
Those kids... were
no ordinary kids.
Not that crap again. Come on,
stop bein' a chicken.
[GUARD B] But they weren't
carryin' any weapons.
How do you explain
how I got these cuts?
They can't possibly be human.
They moved almost like
they were wild animals.
Well, now that you mention it,
that woman was saying
weird stuff like that.
Something about wolves.
About wolves?
That's him.
[HASU]
Oh, crap!
--Hey!
--Hold it!
It's hard to believe
how big you've grown.
Hey, Blue, do you remember this?
Rusu found you somewhere and
brought you home. Look at' cha.
You were nothin' but
a little pup back then.
I told him no again and again,
but he wouldn't listen.
And in the end, he just
stood there in the doorway
not saying a word,
with those big eyes of
his all full of tears.
Ah, damn it, if it's one
thing that kid got from me,
it was my stubbornness.
Well, partner, how many years
would you say it's been?
You're all grown up now,
aren't cha, Blue?
[snoring]
--[clatter]
--[grunting]
[GUARD B]
Stay still, kid!
[HASU]
Let go of me!
I said, let go!
[GUARD B]
You little!
Hey, That's enough!
[growling]
[GUARD B]
Stay... Stay away from me!
Get away from him.
Hey.
Geez, you reek.
Anything in particular?
Hypothetically speaking,
if a member of the House
of Darcia came back,
where exactly do
you think he'd--?
The Darcias?
Now that takes me back.
The family fell into ruin,
and this city died.
It's all their fault.
I doubt if they'll ever
come back here again.
For argument's sake, what if
they happened to come back
to get something that
was truly vital to them?
Something like...
like a Lunar Flower.
Well, the castle may be a mess,
but the Darcia family cemetery
at the foot of the mountain
is still intact.
Of course no one
goes near it now.
You see, just beyond
it lies a dense forest
called the "Forest of Death."
[CHER]
Forest of Death?
[SHOPKEEPER]
Something out there
makes the Earth's
magnetic field go haywire.
They say it makes
humans lose their way.
Thank you, you've
been very helpful.
[SHOPKEEPER]
That's not for sale.
That's a portrait
of Lord Darcia.
It was painted centuries ago.
It's really supposed to be
hanging in the palace,
but I'm keeping an
eye on it for now,
just to make sure
nothing happens to it.
[HASU]
Ow...
Hold still.
So, kid, you live alone?
Isn't it obvious?
[QUENT]
Where's your mom?
She's dead.
[QUENT]
And your dad?
Like they say, nature
makes a fine mother.
[GUARD B]
Well, well, we meet again.
[growling]
[GUARD C]
Would you give it a rest?
[beeping]
Yes, sir.
Ah!
Hey.
You really spooked me back
there before, you know that?
Now I get to return the favor.
Roger that. We're
going back to base!
[whines]
[growling]
[thud]
Now listen to me, kid, I
know it's important for you
to feel like you're makin'
it on your own, but...
[HASU] Oh yeah? And what
would you know about it?
I know.
And so will you when you have
kids of your own some day.
Yeah, I bet I will.
Then, I'll just decide
to take off one day,
sayin' it's for the
good of the family
and when my kid tries to stop
me, I'm just gonna ignore him.
You're like that,
too, aren't you?
[HASU] If you're done with
your good deed for the day,
then just leave me alone.
I'm sick of being
lectured by people
with nothin' better to do.
[QUENT]
Be seeing you, kid.
Sorry I bothered you.
Ah-ha!
What took you so long?
[TOBOE chuckles]
Hey, welcome back.
How did it go?
They've really got us
surrounded this time.
So we'll have to move at night.
There's a place that's
not too far from here
that the local humans
call the Forest of Death.
Forest of Death.
That doesn't sound good.
They say if you get lost
in it, you never come out.
Big deal.
With our noses that forest will
be a piece of cake, am I right?
Right.
How's it lookin'?
[TSUME] I found an escape
route that'll be perfect.
That settles it.
We'll be leaving tonight.
[TOBOE] All right! We can
finally get outta here!
The cemetery of
the House of Darcia.
Forest of Death.
[gasps]
Darcia.
We have the area
surrounded, sir.
Good, get ready
to storm that thing.
Kill everyone in sight
but the target.
Yes, sir.
They're not here!
But how? Where the
hell'd they go?
[GUARD D]
What? Roger.
The Commander says
they got away.
Who got away?
They're here! All forces
quickly converge-- Ah!
[GUARD E]
There they are! Shoot!
[whistles]
That's the boy.
No doubt about it!
[whimpers]
Oh Blue.
Blue, I... Hm?
What the hell
happened to you?
[howling]
I'll be back as soon as
I put an end to this.
Shouldn't they be here?
They are here.
Uh...
But where?
Sorry we're late.
Operation successful.
[HIGE chuckling]
[QUENT] You damn wolves!
You'll never fool me again!
Kiba.
He protected her.
[yelling]
[gunshots]
Blue.
[howling]
[CHEZA] Forest of Death.
Another Apple. Grab the Gorilla.
Trumpet Grass Tides.
Old Wise Owl.
True or Not True?
Man in a Mask. Wonder and Wait.