[laughing]
This feels great.
The sunlight is so peaceful.
How I've missed it.
My love, what're you looking at?
How beautifully your hair
shines in the sunlight.
And your eyes. So gentle.
And so full of love.
I wish to engrave this
image of you in my heart,
so that this moment
will last forever.
But why?
We are always
together, you and I.
And we always will be.
Together until the end of time.
Hamona. Beautiful Hamona.
Dearest, I will
give you my word.
I promise that one day I
will take you to Paradise.
[HAMONA]
No.
For me, this is Paradise.
When you and I are together,
wherever we are,
that is always Paradise to me.
[DARCIA]
Huh?
My Lord, the Lady
Hamona has fallen ill.
Paradise sickness?
[NEIGE]
Her soul is slowly fading away.
[DARCIA]
Are you telling me
she has the curse of my clan?
[DARCIA]
You are my only hope.
You must guide this
miserable soul from despair.
[DARCIA]
Cheza, the Flower Maiden.
[HIGE]
C'mon, runt!
Get a move on or
we'll leave you behind!
[TOBOE] Hey, doesn't this forest
seem kinda strange to you?
There aren't any animals around.
Tell me somethin', you do know
that you're a wolf, right?
[TOBOE]
Huh?
Think about it, genius.
They probably ran off
when they saw us comin'.
Oh, of course.
This is the problem with
takin' city kids to the woods.
I was thinkin'. I haven't
smelled the Flower at all
since we left that cave.
I wonder if this is
really the right way.
You wanna give us a clue here?
Sure.
Where exactly are we headed?
To Paradise.
And just what in the hell
is guiding you there?
I'm goin' on instinct.
Here we go again.
I just wish at least it felt
like we were getting closer.
Not that I'm complaining
or anything.
[distant humming]
That noise.
It's an airship. It must
be the one of the Noble's.
Ugh. I hate that sound.
[DARCIA] We're getting close.
Can you sense it?
That castle is
where you were born.
So they're here.
It's a faint signal,
but it's moving.
Commander, she must be
somewhere inside that vessel.
[COMMANDER]
Can you be certain?
I'm sure. These
readings confirm it.
Cheza is awake and she's
reacting to something.
It's been over a month
since she was stolen.
There's no telling if she's
alive, let alone awake.
[CHER]
He's not going to kill her.
It was him we took her away
from in the first place.
And now, gentlemen, it is our
sole objective to retrieve it.
Fire a warning shot.
[TOBOE yelps]
What's goin' on?!
Man, they're really goin' at it.
She's there.
Hold it! It's nothing to
do with us! Stay out of it!
I can feel it.
Feel what?
I'm not sure.
But it's so familiar.
Come on, don't you guys
feel anything at all?!
Kiba!
Can you?
That guy is hopeless.
[KIBA]
The Flower Maiden.
Look at these readings.
What's it mean?
Target his main engines.
Yes, sir!
Cheza.
Don't do it!
Oh, no!
[TSUME]
Kiba!
[TOBOE]
Wait for us!
That scent.
[sniffing]
The scent is faint,
but it's up there.
Why in the hell are
you so worked up?
Aw, man.
It's got the stink of a
Noble mixed in there, too.
A Noble?
[TOBOE]
Hey, Kiba!
Umm. I got this fluttery
feeling in my chest.
Is that what you meant?
Let's go.
[RETRIEVAL LEADER] The crest
of the House of Darcia.
Was this their stronghold?
[CHER]
From I understand,
this was just one of many
villas the Darcia Family had.
But that was years ago.
Yeah, they were
cursed by Paradise
and the family fell into ruin.
Soon this place'll fall, too.
The town is a match
for the Flower Habitat
that was depicted in
the Book of the Moon.
Cheza was born right here.
Still, it's hard to imagine
that Lunar Flowers ever bloomed
on this devastated mountaintop.
I don't know why, but
my heart is pounding.
And I feel all warm
and tingly inside.
This is that cool feeling y'get
before pouncin'
on a pretty girl.
Don't let your guard down.
But there's shiver
up my spine, too.
[TOBOE gasps]
[ALL gasp]
It's her. It's really her.
My heart just skipped a beat.
Who is that?
Hold on!
Cheza.
We meet... at last.
Aw, I wanna be
held like that.
Can that really be...?
Yeah.
That's her. That's
the Flower Maiden.
[COMMANDER]
What's goin' on?
[CHER]
I don't know.
Whatever it is, it's
coming from the garden.
But the reading's too large,
I can't get an exact fix on it.
Surround the garden immediately!
Mobilize all units now!
[CHEZA]
This way! This way!
That's Cheza, all right.
That's the Flower Maiden.
She's a flower and a maiden?
That's pretty weird.
[HIGE]
Well, the way I heard it,
some Nobles with too
much time on their hands
made her from a Lunar
Flower in a lab somewhere.
[TSUME] They made a
human from a flower?
Give me a break, you
really believe all that?
[HIGE] Come on, she's standin'
right there, isn't she?
[TOBOE]
Yeah.
And she smells nice,
too. Like a flower.
[TSUME] Smell or no smell,
I don't trust any of this.
[TOBOE] Even though your
heart skipped a beat, too?
[HIGE]
Well, I for one believe it.
I mean, just think about it.
As crazy as it
seemed at the time,
Kiba led us straight to
this place on instinct
or whatever you
wanna call it, right?
Even if it is some
big coincidence,
at least it finally feels
like we're one step closer.
[TOBOE]
It sure does.
Well, either way you look at it,
she's really not my type at all.
It's such a bummer.
The signal's definitely moving.
No, of course, I don't know why!
I need you to surround the area
before we lose the signal,
do you understand?!
[CHEZA] This one has
been waiting for you.
[CHEZA] This one was born
right here in this place
for that reason.
Everybody! This one's home!
Oh my. There is...
no one here anymore.
They... They all...
withered and died...
This one... is the
only one left.
[gunshots]
Kiba, we're in serious trouble!
I smell humans all
over the place.
I think we're surrounded.
No! It wasn't her!
C'mon guys, we don't
have time for this!
We have to escape!
Whadd'ya mean escape?
We're surrounded!
Where the hell are
we suppose to go?!
[gasps]
Where are you going?!
Didn't you hear what I said?!
What do we do? Huh?
We don't have much of a choice.
[HIGE groans]
Kiba's lost it this time.
[TOBOE]
Hm?
Kiba, wait for me!
[gunshots]
[CHER]
Are you trying to kill her?
What's going on?
[SQUADMAN]
Sir, we're being attacked by--
[click, static]
Someone is trying
to escape with it.
Darcia.
[COMMANDER]
Hm?
I don't know.
Man. Look at all those guys!
[TSUME]
Damn it.
[thud]
[HIGE]
We're totally screwed!
They've got that end
totally blocked off!
What do we do?
If we left her here,
we could get away.
[gasps] Forget it!
[gunshots]
[TOBOE]
Guys!
[CHEZA]
This way!
[COMMANDER]
Can you confirm how many?
[RETRIEVAL LEADER] Information
is still being gathered, sir.
A couple of reports said
they saw some boys.
Some boys?
[beeping]
Is she close to here?
[gusnhots]
[RETRIEVAL LEADER]
Let's go!
She... She was smiling.
[HIGE]
What the hell?!
It's no use! There's no way
we can get outta here!
We could always
try surrendering.
Heh. I'm kidding, I'm kidding!
[CHEZA]
This way.
Where did that giant
hole come from?
The wall just moved!
Hey, I'm not complainin'.
Let's get outta here.
Tsume, come on!
[RETRIEVAL LEADER]
They vanished?
That's impossible!
Start searching!
[DARCIA]
Night is a time of sleep.
However, there are some
tales that can only be told
in the dead of night.
You seem exhausted as well.