[HIGE]
I've got to admit,
the reason I decided
to stay in this city
was 'cause I caught
wind of something.
[HIGE]
I'd never smelled it before,
but I knew what it was.
The scent of Lunar Flowers.
[sniffing]
[HIGE]
To be honest,
I don't really have that
much to complain about.
I can always find
somethin' to eat,
as long as I'm not too picky.
And even when it's freezin',
which is pretty much
all the time,
I can handle it.
The only thing that kinda sucks
is the total lack of
girls around here.
But on that one particular
day, I felt it, all right.
That dangerous but amazing
scent was calling me,
I just couldn't
leave it alone.
[BABY cooing]
Man, you really screwed up.
I mean,
I have seen one of us get caught
before but never this badly.
[KIBA] I can get out of here
whenever I feel like it.
Uh, huh. So then
why are you in there?
[KIBA] I just needed a place
to rest for a while. That's all.
[laughs] I'm Hige,
it's nice to meet 'cha.
[KIBA]
That's not your true form.
Why do you hide yourself?
[HIGE] So I don't end up
where you are.
These people are terrified
of us. So, you know,
If we look like them, they
pretty much leave us alone.
[KIBA]
You're living a lie
just so you can die a miserable
death in this city?
Gotta do what you can
to survive, right?
Keep lookin' like that, you'll
be back here in no time.
It draws too much attention.
[KIBA] Have you given up
your pride as a wolf?
[HIGE]
Hm?
You're a strange
one, all right.
But having pride doesn't count
for much if you're dead,
y'know?
[HIGE]
Strange ain't the half of it.
The guy's totally clueless
but he still has confidence
coming' out of his ears.
Kiba puts his neck on the line
without a second thought.
I guess it's my own
fault for hangin' out
with someone like that,
but what can ya do?
At any rate, we finally met her.
Cheza, the Flower Maiden.
[DARCIA] There is nothing
to fear. You are awake, now,
at last.
[DARCIA] We can finally
set out on our journey.
[CHEZA coughs]
[HIGE]
This way.
Uh!
[DARCIA]
Wolves?
You have my gratitude,
for it was you who woke her.
[KIBA]
What? Who the hell are you?!
[DARCIA]
The Flower Maiden is mine.
The Maiden?
Is that... Cheza?!
[DARCIA] We'll meet in Paradise.
If we meet again, that is.
[KIBA gasps]
[HIGE]
The scent of flowers was gone.
So we set out in
search of Paradise.
That runt, Toboe joined
us along with Tsume,
whose bark's as bad as his bite,
though it's mostly just a front.
Anyway, we're all
in this together!
Go on, give us your best
shot, we can take it!
Oh, man. I sure am hungry.
Yeah, you could say that again.
[TOBOE] How long it's been
since we ate anything?
I don't know, I guess it's
been about three days or so.
[TSUME] Will you two quit
your whining, already?
It's only been
three stupid days.
[TOBOE] Yeah, but if we
hadn't left the city
we would have something
to eat right now.
[TSUME]
Well, worse comes to worse,
we can always eat each other.
[HIGE, TOBOE]
Huh?!
We could start with the runt,
since he's gotten so weak,
and of course there's always
little porky over there.
[HIGE]
Eh.
Wait a second, how come
Kiba isn't on the menu?
Because the guy's totally
full of crap, that's why.
[DARCIA]
We're getting close.
Can you sense it?
That castle is where
you were born.
[HIGE] It wasn't until
after a whole mess
of other stuff happened
that we met Cheza again.
Uh.
She's there.
Hold it, it's nothing to do
with us, stay out of it!
I can feel it
Feel what?
I'm not sure.
But it's so familiar.
C'mon. Don't you guys
feel anything at all?!
[TSUME]
Kiba!
Can you?
That guy is hopeless.
That scent...
[ALL sigh]
It's her.
It's really her.
My heart just skipped a beat.
Who is that?
[CHEZA]
This way! This way!
That's Cheza, all right.
That's the Flower Maiden.
She's a flower and a maiden?
That's pretty weird.
[HIGE]
The way I heard it,
some Nobles with too much time
on their hands made her
from a Lunar Flower
in a lab somewhere.
Well, either way
you look at it,
she's really not my type
at all. It's such a bummer.
[CHEZA] This one has
been waiting for you.
This one was born
here in this place,
for that reason.
[CHEZA]
Everybody! This one's home!
[CHEZA] Oh, my. There
is no one here anymore.
They all... withered and died.
This one is the
only one left.
[KIBA]
Tell us. Who are you?
[HANABITO] The Hanabito is
what they used to call us.
This one could tell
that from your scent.
But, you are not like this one?
[HANABITO] That is true.
You are not like my kind.
You, my dear are a
perfect creation.
The wolf seeks out the flower,
and the flower
seeks out the wolf.
And yet, no matter
how you feel,
you must not go with them.
[CHEZA]
But, why?
[HANABITO] It will only
lead to destruction.
Kiba, can this one
stay with you?
Is it all right that
this one stays with you?
Cheza, you have
to stay with us.
Hige?
[laughs] Sure, why not?
When you're on a journey,
the more the merrier.
[CHEZA]
Toboe?
[TOBOE laughs]
Tsume?
[exhales]
Fine, you can tag along.
If it gets us to where we're
goin', I can put up with ya.
[HIGE] When Cheza was
with the four of us,
she looked really happy.
We all had a soft spot for her.
And it was obvious that
she liked us, too.
I bet you're hungry, right?
Cheza does not eat bugs.
Well then, what
should we feed her?
What is?
This one is stuffed!
And you?
Um. Sure.
C'mon, Tsume. Have
Cheza pet you, too.
It feels unbelievable!
[HIGE]
Ah, she smells so good!
[TSUME growls]
[KIBA gasps]
[QUENT growls]
[KIBA grunts]
Kiba!
[CHEZA]
Wait. We'll all go... together.
This one can be...
useful, too.
Cheza!
[TSUME]
Damn it!
[HIGE] But out of all of us,
Kiba was the special one.
There's somethin' between
him and Cheza that's,
how can I put it?
Well, it's different from what
the rest of us have with her.
We could all see how
connected they were.
But even so, when we
wolves were with Cheza,
all of us were happy.
[HIGE]
And then... it happened!
[HIGE] Our first full moon
since being with Cheza.
Our hearts were pounding like
they were ready to burst!
So this is it.
Yeah, right about now, I feel
like I could do almost anything!
I mean we've all seen
a full moon before,
but 'cause Cheza's with us, it's
seems different, doesn't it?
Uh! Oh man, I just wanna
howl my head off!
Somethin's about to happen.
[KIBA gasps]
It's the path to Paradise.
Is that really what it is?
Amazing! It's amazing!
The wolves.
It's been a long time.
[TSUME]
That stench... He's a Noble?
What are you doin' here?
[DARCIA]
Was your little dream pleasant?
The one where you were
going to Paradise?
What?!
The time has not yet
come for that.
[DARCIA]
Return to me, Cheza.
[CHEZA gasping]
Get out of our way!
It is futile.
Toboe!
[CHEZA gasping]
Ah, the blood of the wolves.
How magnificent.
[CHEZA gasps]
[CHEZA whimpers]
Kiba.
[CHEZA]
That is enough.
[KIBA grunting]
[KIBA]
Don't go!
D-Don't...
[CHEZA]
It is all right.
[KIBA]
Don't go, Cheza. We're wolves.
We're not afraid to die.
[CHEZA]
This one knows that,
but this one has decided.
It is all right.
Kiba.
This one will surely
protect you.
[KIBA]
Che... za...
[HIGE] What could that
Noble want with Cheza?
I mean, what can a human
possibly hope to accomplish
by trying to get to Paradise?
Not that we really cared.
In the end, there wasn't
anything we could do about it.
Cheza was gone.
[HIGE]
You up an movin' already?
C'mon guys, I know we've
been through a lot,
but why all the moping?
I couldn't sleep, that's why.
Yeah, well, neither could I.
[TSUME growls] You slept
like a dead man, as always.
Look, I'm just as shocked and
frustrated as the rest of you
but none of that is
gonna help us figure out
what the hell to do now.
Are we gonna live
here in a stupor
for the rest of our lives?!
Somebody say somethin', dammit!
Kiba!
You haven't said a single
word to any of us
since everything happened.
[TSUME]
Drop it.
[TOBOE]
Leave him alone.
Kiba was hurt the
worst, remember?
[KIBA]
It's not that.
It's just...
I'm really pissed off.
[THUG A]
She went that way!
[THUG B]
Get her! Come back, dammit!
She's over there!
[ALL gasp]
Wow, what a babe!
[THUG B]
She's got friends.
[THUGS laugh]
[BLUE grunts]
Yeah, so what's it to you?
[HIGE] So, how come those guys
were chasing you, anyway?
[BLUE] I thought that
I should work, y'know?
[HIGE] Work? I've never
given it much thought.
That's how supposed
to be, huh?
But it's hard to let go of,
when that's all
you've ever known.
For my entire life,
I've been at Pop's side,
always wanting to be useful
to him somehow, if I could.
I'll bet, from your
point of view,
choosing to live that way must
sound like complete nonsense.
But the thing is,
I was always happy
being that way.
[BLUE]
If nothing had happened,
I could have stayed
happy forever.
[BLUE]
I don't know what happened,
or if it really was wolves
who killed everyone.
But even so,
that's what Pops believes.
[HIGE]
Man.
And just because of that,
he hates all wolves?
[BLUE] If I had stayed
ignorant of what I was,
I would've been able to remain
at Pop's side forever.
If I had never met that girl,
I could have kept on living
the way I always had been.
If I hadn't learned that
there was some wolf in me.
[HIGE]
So what are you gonna do now?
You want to go back
to that guy?
[BLUE]
I can't go back. If I did,
I'd have to hunt
you guys down again.
[HIGE]
Heh. Sounds nice.
I wouldn't mind being
hunted down by a girl.
I'm usually the one who
does all the chasing.
But, somehow, they always
manage to get away.
Whenever I get in the mood I
always have to take a leak.
Kinda like right now.
Well go somewhere and
do it, that's disgusting.
I'll hold it. It looks like
you're ready to run.
[BLUE laughs]
You're nice. Gross, but nice.
[HIGE]
Yeah. I get that all the time.
[BLUE]
Hey. Why don't you come with me?
[HIGE]
Where to?
Doesn't matter where, does it?
Sounds tempting
[HUBB]
Have you ever wanted to go back
to an earlier part of your life?
To when things were happier?
No matter how difficult
the present may be,
there may come a time when
you find yourself thinking,
boy. I really had
it good back then.