[QUENT]
Huh?
[MAN 1]
It's over... It's all over...
This is it... it's over...
this is the end.
The end of everything...
[MAN 2]
Quit your mumbling, would ya?!
Just shut the hell up!
I can fix this
for some bucks.
[laughing]
Oh yeah, I know
I can make good money
off this little baby!
Jaguara's troops carry
around some pretty nice crap.
[MAN 1]
It'll all vanish...
Soon, everything's
just gonna disappear.
This is it...
The end of the world...!
[MAN 2]
Will you shut up!
Why do you have to
keep babbling on and on
about what all of us
already knows!
It doesn't matter
if we try to run...
There's nowhere to go...
--[MAN 2 gasps]
--[ALL gasp]
[MAN 2] I know somewhere
you can go!
--[QUENT] That's enough!
--[ALL gasp]
[MAN 2]
It ain't gonna end.
Jaguara ain't gonna end!
Even if this whole
stinkin' world does disappear,
she ain't goin' nowhere!
Jaguara is the only
hope any of us have left!
She'll save us, see?
Her keep...
Her keep is
an island of dreams!
Of dreams, huh?
An island of dreams...
[laughs, chokes]
I knew you
had a big mouth
to spout all that crap!
You better not
make one more sound!
[laughing]
It's all over... over!
[gunshot]
[ALL gasping, crying]
[GIRL sobbing]
I told the guy
to shut up...
I warned him not
to make another sound,
but he wouldn't listen.
I told him...
And I told him...
just shut up...
Just shut up!
--[gunshot]
--[MAN screaming]
[MAN continues screaming]
[QUENT]
Stop it! Calm down!
Everything's goin' crazy...
Everything...
[BLUE humming]
Tell me...
How did you
and that old man
get split up
from one another?
Are you that strong
because you're a wolf?
I guess.
The one thing Pops hates more
than anything in this world
is what I am.
But you've been at
his side this whole time,
haven't you?
I'm sorry,
this is strange for me.
I've never had a conversation
with a dog before.
[BLUE] Just think if I'd
been able to do this sooner,
I could've talked to Pops
about all kinds of things.
[CHER]
Are you kidding?
He'd pass out from shock.
Maybe.
[CHER] Shouldn't you
be looking for him?
[BLUE] It's okay.
For now, I'll save Cheza.
That's what you're
after, too, isn't it?
Or are you trying to
rescue Mr. Sensitive?
A bit of both, I guess...
It's just...
I really don't know.
There's still so much
we can't seem to get right.
Who knows what'll
happen in the end.
[TOBOE gasps]
[TOBOE]
Is this... an ocean?
[KIBA]
It's an ice floe.
[TOBOE]
What's an ice floe?
[TSUME]
A frozen sea.
Are we gonna walk across this?
We have to.
It's on the other side.
[TOBOE gasps]
That's cold!
Would you be careful, runt?
You know we're on
top of water here.
[TOBOE]
I know that!
Come on! Let's go!
[TOBOE]
What are you waiting for?!
Hurry up! This cold feels great!
What the hell's
he so happy for?
It's freezing!
He's such a pup.
[HUBB gasps]
[HUBB]
Cheza!
[groans]
[HUBB]
Ch-Cheza!
[HIGE]
Hey!
What the hell
are you waiting for?
Are you scared?
I was just getting
ready to, all right?!
Gettin' ready to do what?
Right...
[TOBOE yelling]
Are these all bird bones?
Or what?
Not so much as a
scrap of meat left on 'em.
Don't worry.
We should find something
in the town up ahead.
Yeah, you're right.
The sooner we put this
frozen dump behind us,
the sooner we can eat.
Hey Toboe,
you still in one piece?
Wha--Well of course I am!
Let's get movin'.
[HIGE] C'mon birds,
let's see some flyin' up there!
[HIGE] Shake a leg, runt!
You're fallin' behind!
I know, I know!
[WOMAN]
You smell nice.
[HUBB]
Huh?
Hello?
Is there someone there
or am I hearin' things?
How did you end up
here, stranger?
[HUBB]
Huh?
Well... if I started
from the beginning,
it would take too long to tell.
[WOMAN]
Then make it short.
Oh... Well, I
was brought here--
[sneezing]
[HUBB]
Excuse me.
I, uh, came from Darcia's keep.
[WOMAN]
Darcia?
What on earth are you
doing in a place like this?
[HUBB gasps]
[WOMAN] I guess you
could call it treason.
What kind of treason?
Do you mean against the Nobles?
Jaguara has detested
my kind for generations.
What do you mean "your kind"?
[WOMAN] To her, we've always
been a terrible nuisance.
You can't be
the only one here.
Where are the other captives?
[WOMAN]
They've all been taken away...
To Jaguara's Great Hall.
Great Hall?
[WOMAN]
And there...
They are all put to death.
[WOMAN] You don't have
to worry about that.
They'll just leave
you here to rot.
Though, my time is almost up.
But why?
Why would she do this?
[WOMAN]
Tell me...
Why do you have
such a lovely scent?
Hm? My scent?
You must be smelling Cheza.
Cheza?
[HUBB]
A Lunar Flower girl.
Uh, I mean...
Then, the Flower Maiden is here?
[WOMAN]
The time has finally come...
[HIGE] Man... It's like
a junk yard for bones.
[TSUME] I've got a
bad feelin' about this...
That may be, but we
still have to pass through it.
I kinda figured you'd
say that. Hm?
Toboe?
What happened to your arm?
[TOBOE]
Huh?
Oh, I uh... must've
bumped into something.
It's just a scratch.
Why don't we
rest for a while.
Don't baby me,
I said I'm fine!
Come on! Daylight's wastin'!
If he's got that much
energy, he must be okay.
But there's no telling what
the smell of fresh blood
will attract.
Look on the bright side.
If something does
decide to show up,
we can always eat it.
All the better
if that something
has a lot of red meat on it.
[TOBOE panting]
[HIGE]
Hey, runt!
You okay over there?
Thanks for askin',
I'm just fine.
[crash]
--[crash]
--[TOBOE gasps]
What the hell...?
Toboe, no!
[HIGE]
Get out of the water!
[KIBA yells]
Bastard!
Kiba!
[TOBOE yelling]
[KIBA]
Toboe, don't do it!
Are you all right?
Yeah, where's Toboe?!
[TSUME]
That damn kid went crazy!
[HIGE] This sucks.
This really sucks.
Why is he taking
so long to come back up?
Come on, Toboe.
Toboe!
[TOBOE growling]
[HIGE]
Toboe!
Are you okay?!
[TSUME]
I can't believe it!
[HIGE]
What got into you?
Something happened...
And then... I just... I just...
I dunno, it was like
something deep inside of me
just snapped all of a sudden.
[SEA MONSTER]
You must be joking...
Not once have I ever been
defeated on this island.
I have been here, protecting
it since long, long ago.
Even when I was
the only one left.
In this world, it's either
kill or be killed.
But understand this...
I will not die a victim...
I am going...
...to save you.
[stomach growls]
Hige...
He's your kill,
so you eat first.
[JAGUARA] I tell you now
the words of Red Moon.
From the Great Spirit
was born the wolf
and man became its messenger.
The beast lives
his life in silence,
abiding where the blessing
of the blood of the gods
is bestowed upon him.
The white Flower,
after winning the favor
of the lord of the night,
will share her scent.
Preordained and
eternal in countenance,
her form is of a
lily-white supple maiden.
She distills and condenses
all of time
until it becomes
a precious, frozen mass.
Only then will appear...
...the wretched beast.
[BLUE]
It's a "girls only" road trip.
Which, of course, invites
every idiot in a pair of pants
to make a pass at you.
[sighs]
Aren't there any decent
guys around here?
Maybe I'll make the
first move for a change.
See what happens when
the tables are turned.