[alarm blaring]
[gasps]
[DARCIA gasps]
[DARCIA]
What have those fools done?
Honey...
do you think something
might've happened?
Fireworks, maybe?
Could be a festival,
my dear Elmira.
Huh?
[slurping]
Fireworks, huh?
I s'pose you're right.
[gasps] Lord Darcia,
you're here.
[NEIGE gasps]
I beg of you...
please forgive me my lord.
[DARCIA whimpers]
[NEIGE] Lady Jaguara's reach
extended even here.
Jaguara...
[NEIGE]
Please forgive me.
I tried, but there was nothing
I could do to protect her.
[CHEZA sings]
Don't do that...
[singing]
[singing continues]
[DARCIA]
Don't do that!
[NEIGE] They say they'll stop at
nothing to kill every last wolf.
Those people don't
know anything.
None of them do...
Hamona...
[HAMONA]
My love.
I wish to see you once more...
Even without the wolves,
there is still this one thing
I have left within me.
I have the eye of the wolf.
I can see you whenever I like.
[HAMONA]
I know we will meet again.
[DARCIA]
Yes,
someday soon.
[HAMONA]
I love you,
Darcia...
My Lord Darcia.
[gasps]
[DARCIA whimpers]
[screams]
[grunting]
[whimpers]
[DARCIA screams]
[THUG A]
Get back here!
[BLUE panting]
What's a'matter baby,
I thought you wanted work.
[BLUE] As if I'd take a job
to please some filthy human!
[THUG B] We paid the broker
good money for you.
Now, be a good girl...
[screams]
[HIGE]
You up an movin' already?
C'mon guys, I know we've
been through a lot,
but why all the moping?
[TOBOE]
I couldn't sleep, that's why.
Yeah, well, neither could I.
[TSUME exhales] You slept
like a dead man, as always.
Look, I'm just as shocked and
frustrated as the rest of you,
but none of that
is gonna help us
figure out what the
hell to do now.
Are we gonna live
here in a stupor
for the rest of our lives?!
Somebody say somethin', dammit!
Kiba! You haven't
said a single word
to any of us since
everything happened.
[TSUME]
Drop it.
[TOBOE]
Leave him alone.
Kiba was hurt the worst,
remember?
[KIBA]
It's not that.
It's just...
I'm really pissed off.
[THUG B]
She went that way!
[THUG A]
Get her!
Come back, dammit!
She's over there!
[footsteps]
[KIBA gasps]
[TOBOE, TSUME gasp]
Wow, what a babe!
[THUG C]
She's got friends.
[THUGS laugh]
Yeah, so what's it to you?
[THUG C]
Hand over the girl.
[HIGE]
Why should we?
[THUG B]
She's our merchandise.
Move.
You guy's aren't from
around here, are ya?
Yeah, so what if we aren't?
There's a big demand for
young bodies in this town.
People will pay top dollar
for healthy organs.
[THUG B grunting]
You don't expect us to give
up our bodies, do ya?!
[THUG B yells]
[THUG C groans]
[THUG A yells]
[whimpering]
I'm goin' crazy.
Oh, no. It's the curse.
It's the curse of
the House of Darcia!
[screams]
[TSUME laughs]
Did you see that stupid
look on their faces?
[TOBOE]
I know. That felt terrific!
Kiba, are you all right?
Yeah.
Hey, are you all right?
Thanks for helping me.
[TSUME]
We didn't do it for you, y'know.
Those idiots just
happened to catch us
in a bad mood, that's all.
She was thankin' us.
Why do you have to be so harsh?
It's not like we run
into girls every day.
By the way, I'm Hige.
My name is...
It's Blue.
It's been a while, huh?
[HIGE]
Huh?
You guys know each other?
[KIBA]
You could say that.
[TSUME] You did some
pretty nasty things to us
when you were with the human.
[TOBOE]
That old guy...
Where is he?
[BLUE]
Something happened and...
we were split up.
[KIBA] He was still trackin' us
in the last city we were in.
I know he was.
That's why he was there.
Pops will track down a wolf
to the ends of the earth.
I don't get it.
Aren't you a wolf, too?
Hey, that girl.
Isn't she with you?
Y'know, the one you guys
were traveling with?
She had a...
a really strange scent.
The girl...?
You mean Cheza?
[BLUE]
Cheza...?
[HIGE]
Oh, uh...
about that, well...
Let's just say we shouldn't talk
about that right now, okay?
I know! Why don't we
look for some food?!
I mean, we did just bump
into each other and all.
Besides, there's a
whole mess of danger
for a girl on her own
in a town like this.
[TSUME]
Not a chance, porky.
Why not?!
[TSUME]
As if I'd ever hang with her.
She was doing everything
she could to hunt us down.
[HIGE]
Yeah, but...
You know you're only saying that
because it didn't happen to you.
[BLUE laughs]
Forget it.
I don't want to hang out with
a bunch of kids, either.
See ya 'round.
[HIGE]
Hey!
Aren't you guys
bein' a little cold?!
Hold on, it's dangerous!
Wait up!
[TOBOE]
But, Hige!!
His tail wags whenever
there's a girl around.
Just let him go.
When we were back in that city,
she found out she was half wolf.
Cheza told her.
[TOBOE]
Half wolf?
[KIBA] That side of
her must've woken up
after meeting Cheza.
[TOBOE]
Cheza.
I wonder what she's doing.
You think she's okay?
[HIGE]
Wait up, will ya?
You should go back.
Your friends are
gonna leave you behind.
That's okay.
Life's pretty borin'
when it's only guys.
[HUBB sighs]
I can't believe it held
together this long.
[BARTENDER] So... You say
you're from Freeze City.
Is that right?
[HUBB]
That's right.
[BARTENDER] Well, if you've
come all this way to find her,
she must've done somethin'
pretty awful, huh?
Yeah, She's a master criminal
with the face of an angel.
Hey, wait.
That's the woman.
You know, the one
who drank like a fish.
You mean, you saw her?
Yeah. She came in
here a while ago.
She was throwin' 'em back
with that old guy over there.
[BARTENDER B]
Mister!
Hey, mister!
[QUENT]
Hm?
[gasps]
You again.
[QUENT] I can't believe she was
the woman you were lookin' for.
[HUBB]
How'd she look?
Was she okay?
[QUENT] Well, considering the
amount of booze she was drinkin,
she seemed fine to me.
Oh, is that so?
You'd be better off
to just give up
on a headstrong
woman like that.
She only seems that way, but
I know how she really is.
I've been at her side for as
long as I can remember.
Believe me, it's a big mistake
to think that you know
everything about
someone just because you're
with them all the time.
So I take it your search for
the wolves is going well.
And where's your dog?
Was she too headstrong for you?
I guess she was.
She ran off on me.
I'm so tired I can
barely think.
It's gotten so bad,
I don't even know what the hell
I've been searchin' for.
Wolves, remember?
Yeah.
It was the wolves.
It's always been wolves.
I'd love to stay and chat, but
I really don't have the time.
Excuse me.
[QUENT] I've always
had this suspicion...
Ever since my boy found
Blue and brought her home,
even though she
was just a pup.
I figured she had some
wolf blood in her.
That's the reason she
was able to track down
the wolves so well.
I've never been
good with drunks.
[TOBOE]
I wonder where Hige ran off to.
[TSUME] Once he gets dumped
he'll come sulking back.
[TOBOE exhales]
I'm gonna go look
around for him.
Just take it easy
till I get back.
[KIBA] That's the same
crest from the castle
where Cheza was held.
[TSUME sighs]
This area
must still be part of
that Noble's territory.
[KIBA] The curse of the
House of Darcia, huh?
What?
That's what the guy back
there said when he saw us.
[TSUME]
Mm.
Humans have always
seen wolves that way.
That's why they're
so scared of us.
Why didn't you let 'em
have it back there?
I would've expected you to jump
at the chance to rip
those humans to pieces.
It's not 'cause of
your injuries, is it.
Even if we had killed 'em,
I doubt they would have
tasted very good.
Can't argue with that.
[HIGE] So, how come those guys
were chasin' you, anyway?
[BLUE] I thought that
I should work, y'know?
[HIGE] Work? I've never
given it much thought.
That's how it's
supposed to be, huh?
But it's hard to let go of, when
that's all you've ever known.
For my entire life,
I've been at Pop's side,
always wanting to be
useful to him somehow,
if I could.
I'll bet from your
point of view,
choosing to live that way must
sound like complete nonsense.
But the thing is,
I was always happy
being that way.
[BLUE]
If nothing had happened,
I could've stayed
happy forever.
[QUENT]
There were wolves.
It was if they were mocking me.
They took away everything in
my life that was precious to me.
[BLUE]
I don't know what happened,
or if it really was wolves
who killed everyone.
But even so...
that's what the Pops believes.
[HIGE]
Man.
And just because of that
he hates all wolves?
[BLUE] If I had stayed
ignorant of what I was,
I would've been able to
remain at Pop's side forever.
If I had never met that girl...
I could have kept on living
the way I always had been.
If I hadn't learned that
there was some wolf in me...
[HIGE]
So what are you gonna do now?
You want to go back
to that guy?
[BLUE]
I can't go back.
If I did, I'd have to
hunt you guys down again.
[HIGE]
Heh. Sounds nice.
I wouldn't mind being
hunted down by a girl.
I'm usually the one
who does all the chasing.
But, somehow, they always
manage to get away.
Whenever I get in the mood,
I always have to take a leak.
Kinda like right now.
Well go somewhere and
do it, that's disgusting.
I'll hold it.
It looks like you're
ready to run.
[BLUE laughs]
You're nice...
Gross, but nice.
[HIGE]
Yeah. I get that all the time.
[BLUE] Hey, why don't
you come with me?
[HIGE]
Where to?
Doesn't matter where, does it?
Sounds tempting...
Huh?
What the hell're
you doin' here?!
I just happened to
be passing by...
[TOBOE laughing]
[gunshot]
[TOBOE]
Uh. Was that a...?
Hige.
[HIGE]
Damn!
Hey! What're you doin'?
We gotta go!
[THUG C laughs]
Well, lookyhere.
We found us some wolves.
Ha. Jaguara's people will pay
us a small fortune for you.
Jaguara?
They're gone...
[TOBOE gasps]
Looks like someone was shot.
--[gunshots]
--[ALL gasp]
[gasps]
[KIBA]
Are you okay?
Don't worry, the bullet
only grazed my arm.
[ELMIRA]
What's the matter?
Have you boys been hurt?
Are you all right?
--[gun cocks]
--Huh?
[OLD MAN]
Elmira...
You come over here, now.
[KIBA] We have no intention of
hurting either one of you.
[ELMIRA] Oh, for heaven's
sake, dear, put the gun down.
They're only children.
[OLD MAN]
Don't be stupid,
they're strays and
they're dangerous!
What are you talking about,
have you lost your senses?!
Elmira, I may be an old man,
but I am not going senile!
Take a close look at those two!
[HIGE]
Uh crap!
[ALL gasp]
We are not gonna
do anything to you.
So just leave us alone.
I don't wanna fight
if there's no reason to.
I don't wanna kill.
[THUG B]
Did ya see the wolves?!
[THUG C]
Search over there!
[TSUME]
Those people want to capture us
and sell us to
the highest bidder.
It's up to you whether
we can avoid bloodshed.
[OLD MAN]
Die, you damn wolves!
Take this!
And this!
Did you kill them?!
[OLD MAN whimpers]
[ELMIRA]
Stop it! That's enough!
They cast a spell on me!
I was only--
[ELMIRA]
Calm down, it's safe now!
Dammit.
Those things are worthless
if they're dead!
[HUBB] Nobody should
ever get married...
Got that right!
A man's better off without
a wife weighin' 'im down.
What the hell is wrong
with being single?!
You can live your
life just fine!
Wives do nothin' but
drive a man crazy.
There's just no
figurin' 'em out.
You think you know 'er, but the
minute the "I do's" are done,
she becomes a different person.
You are so right.
And it's only after the
divorce she loosens up...
No sane man should ever
have a family...
[HUBB]
Damn straight.
You're better off not
having anything...
that's precious to you.
[HUBB]
Oh, Cher,
where are you?
[QUENT]
Hey, Detective Dandy.
[HUBB]
Huh?
[QUENT]
Wanna go up the road?
Check out the next town?
[HUBB]
The what?
[QUENT]
If she was still in the area,
you should've bumped
into her by now.
And since you haven't,
my guess is she's
either gone back home, or she's
moved on to the next city.
Cher would never go back.
Not with the way things are.
[QUENT]
Well, then...
that settles it.
[ELMIRA]
Please forgive my husband.
I can't believe he thought you
were wolves, of all things.
He's starting to get more
and more confused lately.
That's why we came out here
on this little jaunt.
"Let's spend the time we have
left on the road", he said.
So now,
this trailer is our home,
as well as our coffin.
But we've seen such
horrible things.
That castle of the Darcias
to the west of here,
which must have been
beautiful once,
is nothing but a giant grave.
The castle of the Darcias...?
It's as if everything
in this world
has given up its desire to live.
[KIBA]
No, it hasn't.
The old man isn't
confused at all.
He's right.
We are wolves.
Y'ready to go?
[TOBOE]
Mm.
G'bye, mister. Take care.
Where are you going to go?
To the castle in the west.
[QUENT] There are times in your
life when you shouldn't drink.
At work and behind the wheel.
Don't drink when you drive and
don't drive when you drink.
If you ask me,
I say why buy the car
when you can spend the
money on more booze?