[OLD SEER moaning]
[moaning continues]
[OLD SEER] Terror is fierce,
overwhelming fear.
Ye accursed of the earth...
you will be rent asunder
by the poisonous fangs
of the night and dawn
will not come for you.
Ye poor soul,
ravished by heat...
The vast spirit of the light
will never again favor you
with the magnificence and
warmth of her seductive smile.
[OLD SEER]
Hear me...
ye accursed of the earth.
Your benighted world
will never rouse
from its perpetual slumber...
and through devastation,
be lured into a darkness
that transcends the night.
[LORD ORKHAM]
A prophecy of destruction?
This night portends a full moon.
[LORD ORKHAM]
Call out the royal guard.
At once!
[BEBOP]
Mm?
[FEMALE SCIENTIST]
Sorry to keep you waiting.
Come on, let's go.
[sighs]
Just keep walking.
Pretend we're old friends.
Who are you?
I used to work in the same
lab as Doctor Degre.
[gasps] Where've you
been all this time?
I've been trying to track
you people down for weeks,
but it's as if you all vanished.
And every trace of the lab's
existence has been erased.
[FEMALE SCIENTIST]
It was shut down
by agents of the
Intelligence Bureau,
who report directly
to the House of Lords.
But... Why?
It's Cheza.
She was stolen by someone
over a month ago.
[gasps]
[HUBB]
What about Cher?!
Doctor Degre went with
the retrieval team
to help find the flower maiden.
Sorry I don't have any
idea where they went,
but I'm sure the
Doctor's all right.
Why are you...
It's because she used to talk
about you all the time.
I hope you find her.
Thanks for that.
[HEAD DETECTIVE] Let's leave
it at that lovely sentiment,
shall we Detective Lebowski?
[HUBB]
Hm?
[BOTH gasp]
[HEAD DETECTIVE]
I suppose I should call you
by your new title:
"Suspect Lebowski."
The House of Lords
has issued a warrant for
your immediate arrest.
Please... come with me.
[LORD ORKHAM]
You...
You're Jaguara's...
Man, what a seedy-lookin' town.
It's my kind of place.
I bet it is.
Smell the danger in the air.
My blood's on fire.
Me, too, me, too! Uh!
Pretty big talk
for someone's who's
scared all the time.
But that's not the only reason
you're fired up, is it, runt.
For one thing, tonight's--
Yeah. It's a full moon.
[grunts] I know it's
like that for us
'cause we get our strength
from the full moon...
But what about Cheza?
She looks like she's
glowing, too!
Yeah.
"Once a year, on the
night of a full moon
flowers will hear
the moon's call,
and return to Paradise."
That's a legend I heard once.
So... you mean
tonight, she'll...
I'm not sure if
it'll be tonight.
We'll just have to wait and see.
[TOBOE] What? What's
gonna happen to her?
You're not sayin' that Cheza's
gonna bloom or somethin',
are ya?
[CHEZA]
This one is excited, too!
[HUBB groans]
Tell me, what exactly
were you thinking,
carrying around a
banned book like this?
You say you're
looking for a woman
who divorced you.
But Lebowski...
There's no corroborative
evidence that such a woman
ever existed in this city.
[HUBB]
Uh!
[HEAD DETECTIVE] In fact,
there are no records anywhere
that prove you were
ever married.
[HUBB exhales]
[HEAD DETECTIVE]
Lebowski...
Thanks to the protection
of Lord Orkham,
we've all been able to
eke out a substantial
living for ourselves.
What the hell happened to you?
Correct me if I'm wrong,
but wasn't it your policy
to do everything you could
to stay out of trouble?
Yes it was, but
something's changed.
Either me, or else the world.
What?
[HUBB] You spend your whole
life licking the Noble's boots
and what does it get you?
Once you become a liability,
you're abandoned,
just like I've been.
Lord or no, Orkham is nothing
but a cowardly old man.
Tell me, did being beaten
at his own game
by that fallen Noble really
upset him that much?
If you mean Darcia, we
already shot him down!
Darcia...?
But you haven't found
them yet, have you?
Darcia, or Cheza.
[HUBB groans]
Darcia's Aerial City
might be protecting him,
along with his accomplices!
But it's only a matter of
time before we find them!
Thanks for clearing that up.
Can I ask you one more thing?
What?! What is it?!
[HUBB] This... "Darcia."
Which Darcia do you mean?
[HEAD DETECTIVE growls]
You know which!
The Darcia in here,
in this book!
Ah.
[explosion]
[alarm blaring]
[phone rings]
[HEAD DETECTIVE]
Yes? Yeah.
What?
Combat units?
What do you mean?
An invasion?!
Uh! Lord Orkham is what?!
Hubb. Are you all right?
[HUBB] Don't worry,
its not you're fault.
But still... how
did this happen?
I guess I was deceived...
Do you mean by wolves?
What the hell's goin' on?
[groans]
Sorry, pal.
[MAN A]
What's going on?!
[POLICEMEN shouting]
[HEAD DETECTIVE groans]
Hey! You all right?
[POLICEMAN]
What happened?
I don't know.
He suddenly collapsed.
Sorry, but, uh... could
you take care of it?
[COMMANDER]
What's happened?!
I want a status
report, right now!
[RETRIEVAL GUARD C]
Sir. Lord Orkham, he's...
He's been assassinated!
[BOTH gasp]
[RETRIEVAL GUARD C]
Lady Jaguara's combat units
have taken control of the keep.
Reports say that our remaining
forces are still engaging them
in the surrounding city.
Your orders, sir?
[COMMANDER]
Direct all squads to withdraw.
We've got more important
things to do right now
than look for
some flower girl!
We will attack Jaguara!
[RETRIEVAL LEADER]
But sir...
What about our mission?
With Lord Orkham gone,
our city could suffer the same
ruinous fate as this one.
Do you really want
that to happen?
[MEN]
No, sir!
[CHER]
It's magnificent...!
If I had use of this device,
I would be able to tap into
and communicate
directly with her mind.
Just as it was written
in the Book of the Moon.
--[door closing]
--[gasping]
It would appear that
I have granted you
too much freedom.
The time for dalliance is over.
You have soothed the loneliness
of my isolation long enough.
I must go now, and retrieve
the Flower Maiden.
Uh! Tell me! Do you
know where she is?!
I can sense Cheza's presence
within my very soul.
Tonight we will see a full moon.
[CHER whimpers]
So this is it.
Yeah. Right about now, I feel
like I could do almost anything!
I mean we've all seen
a full moon before,
but 'cause Cheza's with us, it's
seems different, doesn't it?
Ah! Oh, man, I just wanna
howl my head off!
Something's about to happen...
[howling]
[DARCIA]
The Book of the Moon.
For my clan, that was where
all of this first started.
[DARCIA] Within its pages lies
my grandfather's research.
An accumulation of the finest
alchemy of his day.
And every last bit of it
was intended to be a means
of reaching Paradise.
My grandfather disappeared
into Paradise.
But what, exactly, is Paradise?
[DARCIA] It is a world where
wolves reign supreme.
[CHER gasping]
Paradise will save me.
It will lift the horrid
curse that is upon me,
and that of the woman I love.
My beloved Hamona was ravaged
by what is called
Paradise sickness.
Her soul was stolen by Paradise,
yet she still lives.
[DARCIA]
Her skin has lost
the warmth that yours
still possesses.
Are you sure you should be
telling me all of your secrets?
[DARCIA]
Hm.
You may wait for me here.
[CHER whimpers]
[DARCIA]
Until I return with Cheza.
My Lord Darcia. It appears
Lord Orkham's keep has fallen.
As I thought. Jaguara
has made her move?
So it would seem.
The time is ripe...
It's the path to Paradise...
Is that really what it is?
Amazing! It's amazing!
[gasping]
The wolves.
It's been a long time.
[TSUME]
That stench. He's a Noble...?
What are you doin' here?
Was your little dream pleasant?
The one where you were
going to Paradise?
What?!
The time has not
yet come for that.
[DARCIA]
Return to me...
Cheza...
[whimpers]
Get out of our way!
It is futile.
[gasps]
Toboe!
[CHEZA gasps]
Ah, the blood of the
wolves. How magnificent.
[CHEZA gasps]
Kiba...
[CHEZA]
That is enough.
[KIBA]
Don't go...!
D... Don't...
[CHEZA]
It is all right.
[KIBA]
Don't go, Cheza.
We're wolves...
We're not afraid to die.
[CHEZA]
This one knows that.
But this one has decided.
It is all right.
Kiba... This one...
will surely protect you.
[KIBA pants]
Che... za...
[KIBA]
Cheza...
Lord Darcia. Aerial city, huh?
[HUBB]
Hm? [gasps]
Hi. Lebowski here.
Personal circumstances have
forced me to resign from my job.
Spring has sprung so I'm
setting out on a journey,
where I'm sure only pleasant
encounters await me.