[QUENT]
Blue! Don't go too far!
[BARTENDER]
Wolves? Heh.
I haven't heard about them
since my Grandpa was alive.
He always used to tell me
when the world finally
comes to an end,
Paradise will appear
on the Earth.
But, the trouble is
that only wolves
would know
where to find it.
Who knows...
maybe the world is coming
to an end right now.
[thud]
Wolves are only
servants of Death!
Don't you believe all
that pagan garbage!
Relax, old man.
Wolves have been
extinct for 200 years!
It's just a kid's fairy tale.
[QUENT] The thing
about a fairy tales is,
there's always
some truth in 'em.
[HUBB]
My name is Hubb Lebowski.
I'm a detective on the
Freeze City police force.
Or, at least, I used to be...
My life was pretty
straight forward,
but after meeting this man,
all of that changed.
[HUBB]
Quent Yaiden.
So, tell me,
what brings the sheriff of
Kyrios to our humble city?
That's a heavy artillery
you've got, there.
But I doubt you came all
this way for the hunting.
[QUENT]
What did you do with it?
Where's the animal I put down?
[HUBB]
Dead, apparently.
[QUENT]
Huh?
[HUBB] The carcass will
be disposed of here.
That's impossible!
There's not a chance in
hell that thing is dead.
Don't you get it, it's a wolf!
You think it's a wolf?
[QUENT] It may look like a dog,
but it's not. It's a wolf!
These wolves exist and we
have to destroy them all!
So, do you think
it's really a wolf?
[CHER]
I don't know.
I've never seen a
real one before.
But if it is a wolf...
it may be what's causing
the sudden reaction in Cheza.
[HUBB]
Oh, please. Not Cheza again...
What's that mean?
It's because of her
you and I broke up.
[HUBB]
Cheza.
The crowning achievement
of an ancient alchemy.
My wife... uh... my ex-wife
was among those in charge
of a top-secret research
project for one of the Nobles.
The Flower Maiden
and the wolves,
two being that existed
only in legend.
Was that animal really a wolf?
[HUBB] It's gone. Do you
think someone stole it?
Could be. Or, maybe it
escaped on it's own.
[QUENT] You're obsessed
with the wolves, huh?
Heh, heh. You're dyin'
to know everything, now.
Isn't that right, Detective.
The dog you shot ran away.
What a surprise.
And you think it put some kind
of a spell on us to escape?
You got it.
There's a lot more
of 'em, y' know.
People you pass everyday on
the street or in the market...
The poor slob sittin'
next to you in a bar.
Any one of 'em could be a wolf.
"I tell you now the
words of Red Moon.
From the Great Spirit
was born the wolf
and man became its messenger."
In other words, the human
race was created from wolves.
So says the author of
the Book of the Moon.
Book of the Moon?
I guess I might as well say it.
Instead of lookin' for wolves,
you oughta start
suspecting humans.
Everything's fine.
The lab's power supply is
independent from the main grid.
[DARCIA]
Yes, I know.
[CHER]
Uh!
[DARCIA] Cheza, is not vital
to you. Is that correct?
Uh. Who are you?
[DARCIA]
Everyone is resting now.
You look exhausted as well.
[DARCIA] So tired. You
should rest a while...
[HUBB] Cher disappeared, leaving
me the key to her apartment.
[HUBB] In the midst of all
that neatness and order,
I found something.
the Book of the Moon.
An arcane volume written
by Darcia the First,
an alchemist of
unparalleled genius
who had vanished
over 200 years ago.
Why was it here?
What was Cher doing with a
book that was now banned?
It's a faint signal,
but it's moving.
Commander. She must be
somewhere inside that vessel.
[COMMANDER]
Can you be certain?
I'm sure. These readings
confirm it.
Cheza's awake and she's
reacting to something.
[DARCIA]
Don't do it!
Oh, no!
I can't believe that 10
of our men were injured
while we let them escape.
But they won't be able
to get away from us,
not from this aerial city.
[CHER] Commander, who do you
think those boys really are?
[COMMANDER]
I would imagine
they're some of Lord
Darcia's people.
To be honest, I am not so sure.
That expression,
that the Flower Maiden had
her own face when she was
running with those boys.
Cheza was smiling.
She was smiling, as if
she were truly happy.
[gasps]
[CHER gasping]
[CHER] Have you heard of how
wolves might still be alive,
even today?
[COMMANDER]
No, I haven't.
[CHER]
There's very real possibility
that these boys we saw,
aren't ordinary humans.
They could be wolves who've
learned to survive
by deceiving us.
[MEN cheering]
A glass of whatever'll
warm me up.
[BARTENDER B]
Yes, sir.
I'd like a chilled
sherry, please.
[BARTENDER B]
Yes, ma'am.
[BOTH exhale]
Hit me again.
[HUBB] I don't know
how long it's been
since I started
searching for Cher.
The lab where she
worked was shut down
and all the researchers
had gone into hiding.
I even took a stab at
getting information
concerning the Nobles.
At that point I would have
risked almost anything,
and then, finally...
I got a lead.
[sighs]
It's Cheza. She was stolen by
someone over a month ago.
[HUBB gasps]
[HUBB]
What about Cher?!
Doctor Degre went with
the retrieval team
to help find the flower maiden.
[HEAD DETECTIVE]
Let's just leave it at that,
shall we, Detective Lebowski?
[HUBB grunts]
The House of Lords
has issued a warrant
for your immediate arrest.
Please, come with me.
[HEAD DETECTIVE]
An invasion?!
But, Lord Orkham is what?!
[DETECTIVE]
Hubb! Are you all right?
Don't worry, it's
not you're fault.
But still... how
did this happen?
I guess I was deceived...
Do you mean by wolves?
[explosion]
What the hell's goin' on?
[DETECTIVE yelps]
Sorry, pal.
[DARCIA] The Book of the
Moon. For my clan...
that was where all of
this first started.
Within its pages lies
my grandfather's research,
an accumulation of the finest
alchemy of his day.
And every last bit of it
was intended to be a means
of reaching Paradise.
My grandfather...
disappeared into Paradise.
But what exactly is Paradise?
[DARCIA] It is a world
where wolves reign supreme.
[gasps]
Paradise will save me.
It will lift the horrid
curse that is upon me,
and that of the woman I love.
[DARCIA]
My beloved, Hamona,
was ravaged by what is
called Paradise sickness.
Her soul was stolen by
Paradise, yet she still lives.
Her skin has lost the warmth
that yours still possesses.
My Lord Darcia, it appears
Lord Orkham's keep has fallen.
As I thought. Jaguara
has made her move.
The time is ripe.
Lord Darcia. Aerial city, huh?
Hm?
[gasps]
[HUBB]
Wolves,
the Flower Maiden,
and the blood red moon.
One by one, everything
that was written
in the Book of the Moon
is coming true.
Is this really the
end of the world?
[gasps]
[gasps] Lord Darcia,
you're here.
[NEIGE] Lady Jaguara's
reach extended even here.
Jaguara.
[NEIGE]
Please forgive me.
I tried, but there was nothing
I could do to protect her.
[DARCIA yells]
[BARTENDER A] Well, If you've
come all this way to find her,
she must've done something
pretty awful, huh?
Yeah. She's a master criminal
with a face of the angel.
Hey, wait. That's the woman.
You know, the one
who drank like a fish.
Y'mean, you saw her?
[BARTENDER B]
She was throwin' 'em back
with that old guy over there.
Uh!
You again.
So, I take it your search for
the wolves is going well.
And where's your dog? Was she
too headstrong for you?
[QUENT] I guess she was.
She ran off on me.
[QUENT] I've always
had this suspicion...
Ever since my boy found
Blue and brought her home,
even though she
was just a pup.
I figured she had some
wolf blood in her.
That's the reason she was able
to track down the
wolves so well.
Wanna go up the road?
Check out the next town?
The what?
[QUENT]
If she was still in the area,
you should've bumped
into her by now.
And since you haven't, my guess
is she's either gone back home,
or she's moved on
to the next city.
Cher would never go back. Not
with the way things they are.
[QUENT]
Well then, that settles it.
Hubb!
Cher!
Hubb, what are you...?
How did you...?
Is this a dream?
I can't tell.
I've had so many
dreams about you.
[sneezes]
I met him. I met Darcia.
[HUBB gasps]
[CHER]
I'm sorry, Hubb.
I can't tell you how happy I am
that you came all
this way to find me.
But I have to go.
But why, Cher?!
[CHER]
Please, try and understand.
I have to find out
Cheza's true purpose.
I'm being drawn to
something, Hubb,
and I need to know what it is.
All right, then
I'll go with you.
Then why the hell did you leave
this thing for me to read?!
I'm going with you.
What is it?
Hey!
[DARCIA]
It's because of you.
You and your kind stole
everything from me.
And in return you
gave me a curse.
And grief.
And suffering.
And my eye transformed
into one such as yours.
The price I paid for being
cursed by Paradise.
And now, the only thing
that surrounds me...
is despair.
[KIBA] Don't! What is it,
what do you want?!
[DARCIA] Have you found it?
Have you found Paradise?
[KIBA]
We will. No matter what!
[DARCIA] And what do you
expect to find there?
[KIBA]
A future.
[DARCIA]
A future...?
[KIBA]
Not hope, or despair.
Just a future. Nothin' more.
I no longer have any need...
for a... future.
It's over, wolf.
No, don't!
[gasps]
B-Blue...
My Lord Darcia!
[KIBA]
Cheza!
[TSUME]
Kiba!
Cheza!
Blue, no!
How could you...?
Why, Blue...?
Blue!
[CHER]
Jaguara!
[growling]
[BLUE]
That way!
[CHER gasps]
Did that wolf just
say something?
[CHER whimpers]
[DARCIA]
I can see you whenever I like.
[HAMONA]
I know we will meet again...
[DARCIA]
Yes... someday soon...
[HAMONA]
I love you... Darcia...
[KIBA] They say there's no
such place as Paradise.
Even if you search to
the ends of the earth,
there's nothing there.
No matter how
far you walk,
it's always the same road.
It just goes on and on.
But in spite of that, why
am I so driven to find it?
[KIBA]
A voice calls to me. It says...
"Search for Paradise."
[KIBA]
I'm afraid you're out of luck.
You will not find what you seek
and those you await
will not come.
But there is a hint
of new love in the air.
Now's when your honesty
will be put to the test.
Your lucky color is white.