[HIGE] We have to run away
from here, fast!
[BLUE]
Run away? To where?!
It doesn't matter where!
We never should have
come to this stupid city
in the first place!
[TSUME gasps]
[banging noise]
[banging continues]
Stop that.
You're hurting
yourself for no reason.
[WOMAN] They all tried
to get out that way...
But it was useless.
[TSUME]
Who's "they"?
They captured my entire pack
and brought us
back to this place.
There were many others
who were caught, too.
The only wolf they spared from
was the one wearing the collar.
What did you say?!
That bastard betrayed
every one of us.
[TSUME gasps]
[BLUE]
Hige?!
[HIGE]
Don't follow me!
[HIGE laughing]
Hige...
[HIGE groaning]
[BLUE]
Hige!
What's going on?
Please, what happened to you?
Hey... come on!
Quit playing around!
You have to get up!
Toboe needs our help!
Hige!
[BLUE]
No...
Come on, you've
got to wake up!
Don't do this!
Don't you die on me!
You can't...
Please don't leave me...
[BLUE crying]
Hige...
Hey, Blue...
Do me a favor, will ya?
My collar...
Your what?
[HIGE] Would you take
this collar off of me?
[WOMAN]
My pack was relatively small,
but we managed all right.
Everyone looked out
for one another.
Whenever we came upon a stray,
we tried to make them feel
like they were one of our own.
So naturally,
when he came along,
we took him in without
a second thought.
We shared our food,
our beds, everything.
We should have known...
Soon after we met him,
we started getting attacked
by soldiers without warning.
No matter where we hid,
or how far we ran,
they'd find us.
When we came here,
we finally figured it out.
We knew then that it
was all because of him.
[BLUE growling]
It's okay...
just forget about it.
No way!
If this stupid thing is
what's been hurting you,
I have to get it off!
Y'know what?
You're a great woman.
Don't start talking
crazy on me now...
I've been so blind...
It's funny...
There's so much
I never understood...
But now it all makes sense.
Hige...
My memories weren't real...
None of them...
Everything was just a lie.
[BOTH gasp]
[SOLDIERS yell]
[BLUE gasps]
Blue!
That bastard got lucky.
[QUENT]
Hey, Mr. Wolf Hunters!
[SOLDIERS]
Huh?
What's that ya got there?
It's none of your business.
Come on. Let's go.
I wanna know why you
guys have been capturing wolves.
We're protecting our people.
And securing the city.
[QUENT chuckles]
That recruiting poster
crap doesn't work with me.
Laugh all you want, old man.
Those things are
extinct because of us.
That's where you're wrong.
There's still more
of 'em hiding out there.
Is everyone blind
in this place but me?
Water... Give me water...
[door opens]
[WOMAN gasps]
[TOBOE]
Let go! Let go of me!
[TSUME gasps]
Toboe!
Tsume! I said let go!
[TOBOE groaning]
Come on. Please let me out.
What's gonna happen to me?
[HUBB sneezes]
Wait a minute... That lady...
She was a wolf?
[door closes]
Tsume...
What happened to Hige?
[TOBOE] I don't know.
We got split up.
Where's Kiba?
I thought he was with you.
He's probably somewhere
inside the keep.
[TOBOE] You don't think
he's been killed, do you?
If anything had happened,
I'm sure we would have felt it.
Kiba's alive... He has to be!
[HUBB gasps]
What do you think's
gonna happen to us?
If we won't do somethin',
we'll all get split up and we
won't be able to save Cheza.
[TOBOE]
What are we gonna do?
What'll we do?!
[TSUME]
I don't know...
But none of that's gonna matter
if we don't get out of here.
But how, Tsume?
They're gonna come back and
kill us just like that old lady.
We'll never see
the others again...
You're starting to whine, runt.
[TOBOE] We wont' get
to Paradise either!
[TSUME] We are going to
Paradise, do you hear me?!
I'll be damned if
I let it end like this.
Excuse me...
Are the two of you wolves?
You are, aren't you...
So what?
Who the hell're you?
[HUBB]
Everything that was written
in the Book of the Moon...
Is it true?
Hey, Mister...
How come you're locked up
in here? You're a human.
[HUBB chuckles]
If you're looking
for Cheza, I was with her.
[BOTH gasp]
[HUBB] The soldiers
brought us here together.
But I don't know where
they're keeping her.
[TOBOE] We've got
to get out of here now!
[JAGUARA]
Can you sense it, my dear?
This feeling of joy
within my heart?
Everything is about to begin...
Yes...
He will come.
Soon, my beloved will
come to me at last.
[KIBA]
Cheza...
Are you all right?
At last... I finally
found you...
[KIBA]
Why won't you answer me?!
[JAGUARA]
The white wolf...
[KIBA]
You are the one.
The wolf chosen by the Flower.
How beautiful you are.
Come. Open your eyes.
Open them for my Paradise.
[CHEZA]
Kiba...
My prayers have been
answered. Cheza.
We must feast in celebration,
don't you think?
[JAGUARA laughing]
Have you seen Blue anywhere?
Why would I ask when I can't
understand the answer?
I've seen 'em, you know.
The wolves.
They're in this city.
You've had too much
to drink, old man.
"I shall tell you now
the words of Red Moon."
[SOLDIER B]
Huh?
"Only then will appear
the wretched beast"!
The wolves are everywhere!
They're here,
can't you see them?
What the hell is wrong
with you people?
Have they got you all
under their spell?
Open your eyes,
you spineless coward!
There are wolves all around you!
All over the city!
All over the world!
Open your ey--
Dumb old fart. Think we
should throw him into jail?
This isn't the time to bother
with a nuisance like him.
Not when Paradise
is about to open.
[QUENT] Did he say Paradise...
is... opening?
[CHER]
Darcia...
Wait!
[DARCIA] Will you follow me
into the very heart of darkness?
The preparations
are now complete.
Tell me, am I not beautiful?
Of course, you are, my lady.
For the final rite, we will
stoke the Moonlight Crucible
with the white wolf's blood.
Can you tell me what's
about to happen?
[CHEZA]
Kiba... Kiba... Are you alive?
[KIBA]
Cheza...
Cheza... Sing for me.
[CHEZA singing]
It's Cheza.
I can hear Cheza's song.
Her song?
But why is she crying like that?
I don't know. It's so sad.
Are you hearing Cheza's voice?
You'd both be willing
to die for her.
Why would wolves
sacrifice so much?
[singing]
Welcome to the great feast!
Tonight, Jaguara's Paradise
will be loosed upon the world!
[cheering]
[HIGE] I'm sorry
I made you run so much.
[BLUE]
It's okay.
[HIGE]
Blue. I have to go.
[BLUE] You're gonna
save them, aren't you?
Yeah. I have to at least try.
I guess,
I always thought it was luck
that brought me to them.
What a joke.
I was nothin' but trouble for
those guys from the beginning.
[BLUE]
That's not true.
Yes it is.
But I honestly didn't
remember anything.
I just thought we could all
make it to Paradise.
The whole way here, that's all
that was goin' through my mind.
And then we ended
up in this place.
That's why I have to go.
Then I'll go with you.
I knew you would say that.
But I can't let you.
Why not?
[HIGE]
I need you to wait here.
No, Hige! Don't leave me behind!
I won't! Please, Blue.
If I know you're waiting for me,
I'll make it back
no matter what!
It's the only thing that
can get me through this.
If I know you're here,
I won't give up.
I'll do whatever it takes
to come back to you.
I promise. I'll never
leave you alone, Blue.
[KIBA]
Cheza!
[HUBB]
What is Paradise like, I wonder?
I'm sure each of us has
his own version of it.
For me, Paradise would be
where my beloved wife and I
could treasure our time
alone together... Ha...
Come on, what are you
making me read here?