[CHEZA]
Kiba!
Who's there...?
[TSUME]
Kiba.
[HIGE]
[TOBOE]
Kiba.
[KIBA grunts]
Who's there? Where are
you, I can't see.
[OWL]
Who.
[KIBA]
Uh.
[OWL] Who are you?
Where are you?
I don't know. Who!
[IYEK]
Beyond those rocks
is a land called the
"Desert's Bones."
[TSUME]
The "Desert's Bones"?
[IYEK] If your friend
really did go in there,
looking for him
won't do any good.
Why don't you all stay
here and live with us?
I'm afraid we can't do that.
Y'see our friend is the one who
was looking for Paradise.
See ya 'round. Let's go.
I'm not going.
I want...
I wanna stay here!
You're gonna stay here, huh?
So, does that mean you don't
want to be with us anymore?
[TOBOE]
Yeah.
There's something
about this place,
how Iyek and his people live,
that's Paradise to me.
Are you sure?
Toboe, Is this what you want?
Well, if that's really
what you've decided,
then it's okay by me, kid.
[HIGE]
Hey!
[TSUME]
Take care of yourself.
Since the day I met him,
that kid's wanted
to be with humans.
[HIGE]
Tsume?
The runt's always had
a soft spot for 'em.
I guess that was pretty obvious.
[TSUME] Didn't you say you'd
given up on Paradise, too?
[TSUME] Don't feel like you
have to tag along for my sake.
You'd keep goin', even if
you had to do it alone?
[TSUME]
I want to see it for myself.
If wolves really do
cause the world to end,
then I wanna be there
when it happens.
Besides...
There's no way
I'm givin' up now,
not after spending time
with that pigheaded jerk.
So, I'm gonna look for him.
[HIGE]
Hey, Tsume.
When did you start
talking like that?
You sound like him.
[MEW]
Kiba? What's wrong?
[KIBA]
I can't remember...
I've been hearing all these
different voices... But,
I can't remember
who they belong to.
I feel like I should know them,
but I can't see their faces.
Your memory fades,
little by little.
And then, you get used to it.
[OWL] Yes, little by little,
and little by little, still,
then little by little...
[MEW]
Don't worry, Kiba. I'm with you.
I'll always be with you.
[KIBA]
Sure.
[OWL] Where are you?
Who are you?
Whether alive, or
whether you're dead,
there is nothing.
Nothing matters...
[OWL] The answers are
buried beneath the sand.
Hoo.
[GRANNY]
Toboe.
Toboe!
[GRANNY] That's my good boy.
Are you ready to eat?
[GRANNY] Now, now,
calm down. Stop that!
[GRANNY] Toboe... please...
I can't breath...
[HORSE]
Are you sure?
[TOBOE]
Hm?
Oh, it's you.
[HORSE] About not going
to Paradise, I mean.
I'm sure. I don't really
have what it takes.
[HORSE laughs] Does anyone
ever have what it takes?
It's no wonder they all
think I'm a coward.
Not that it matters any.
[TOBOE] I'm sure Kiba
will be all right.
And it's not like I have to
worry about Tsume or Hige...
I mean, all I ever did
was hold them back.
They don't need that.
If I'm here, I won't
get in their way.
[HIGE]
Man, talk about a wasteland.
Is that it?
[BOTH gasp]
It's those guys!
[TOBOE]
Oh, no!
[IYEK]
Do you sense something?!
[TOBOE] It's coming from
where Tusme and Hige went.
Something is definitely wrong.
I think it might be them.
You mean the people who
attacked the dogs?
[TOBOE]
And attacked us, too.
[IYEK grunts]
The way they're comin'
it's almost like they can track
our moves before we make 'em.
Which means, it's kind of
pointless to run and hide.
[SOLDIER 1 yelps]
[SOLDIER 2 groans]
[TSUME gasps]
[HIGE grunts]
[BOTH panting]
[gasps]
Kiba!
[IYEK]
Stay back!
Don't get any closer.
The poison from that
grass has paralyzed him.
But he can't be! He can't!
He isn't dead!
Maybe not yet, but if we
don't pull him outta there,
he's gonna...
Your friend's spirit
has been taken.
I'm sure the elder
can call it back.
[TOBOE]
Hurry!
[ELDER chanting]
[chanting continues]
[KIBA grunts]
[MEW]
Stop it.
Why, Mew? What's wrong?
It looks like someone
has found you.
[KIBA]
What do you mean?
[MEW gasps]
--[ELDER chanting]
--[KIBA gasps]
[chanting continues]
I wanted to be with you forever.
But now... I know you
shouldn't stay.
You're right.
This place... it isn't
Paradise at all.
[KIBA whimpers]
It's a world where
time no longer exists.
[MEW] Eventually, you
won't remember anything.
Or even why you're here.
You'll forget.
Just like I have.
Why are you doing this?
Kiba. You have to go.
No, wait! Come with me.
Mew.
You and I are more
different than you realize.
Mew! Uh!
[MEW]
Goodbye. Goodbye Kiba.
[gasps]
[CHEZA]
Kiba.
Do you know who this one is?
Kiba, remember!
Cheza.
[CHEZA cries]
Kiba.
Remember us?
Kiba. Kiba!
[KIBA]
Hey guys. Long time no see.
[TOBOE, HIGE sigh]
I suppose you think
that's funny, huh?!
You scared us half to death!
Where've you been?
[KIBA] Someplace peaceful.
It was almost like Paradise.
But... It wasn't, right?
[KIBA]
No. They kicked me out.
[ALL gasp]
Do not worry.
Your friend has returned to you.
[TSUME, HIGE, TOBOE sigh]
[TSUME] We should leave once
Kiba's back on his feet.
[HIGE]
What do you wanna do, runt?
[TOBOE]
Mm...
[TSUME] No matter how
hard you try to hide,
at some point you'll
have to fight.
Like it or not,
that's just the way it is.
I know. I know that.
[TSUME]
You okay now?
[KIBA]
Yeah. Guess I overslept.
I feel like I've been dreaming
for a really long time.
A strange and wonderful dream.
[ELDER] What your spirit beheld
was the Garden of Eternity.
[KIBA]
Garden of Eternity?
[ELDER] You experienced
joy and tranquility
unlike any you've
known before, yes?
[KIBA]
Yeah.
That is enough to
satisfy most people.
They embrace the illusion
and never look back.
But for you, that bliss
was not enough...
Or you wouldn't have returned.
[KIBA] Yes. There's somewhere
else I need to go.
Tell me. Why are you
searching for Paradise?
I have to, to survive.
I see.
[TSUME] So what happened to
you in that "garden" place?
[KIBA]
Nothing.
Except, I met a nice girl.
[HIGE]
You? Met a girl?! No way!
I should'a guessed.
No wonder you seem less uptight.
Wait. I don't get it...
And you won't for a few years.
[HIGE] Oh, man, Kiba
has all the luck...
[TOBOE]
But why can't I get it now?
When I was there,
the whole time it felt like
I was forgetting something.
Y'mean Cheza?
[KIBA]
Not just her. I mean you guys.
Huh?
I... thought your were dead.
You've gotta be kidding?!
Do you have any idea how
hard we busted our butts
tryin' to find you?!
[KIBA] Oh, ya did?
Sorry, I didn't know.
That brain of yours is never
gonna change, is it?
[HIGE laughs]
[ALL laughing]
Let's go.
[TOBOE]
I...
I'm not gonna whine anymore.
And I won't run away.
[HIGE]
Wanna bet?
No way.
You ready? The kid sure is.
Yeah.
[IYEK]
Is Paradise far from here?
[KIBA]
I don't know.
But there's no doubt in my
mind we're gonna find it.
[TOBOE]
Do you think it's okay,
that we're trying to get there?
Take comfort in knowing
that the spirits are with you.
[KIBA]
See ya.
[IYEK]
Sure.
[TSUME]
Let's go.
[HIGE]
Later.
[TOBOE]
Well, guess this is goodbye.
[HORSE] You've got what it
takes to get to Paradise,
and then some.
Thanks a lot.
[HORSE laughs]
[TOBOE laughs]
[TOBOE]
Iyek?
There's something I
need you to do for me.
He's got my scent on him,
so he shouldn't be
too hard to find.
[stomach growling]
[QUENT]
Ah, shut up.
No matter where I am,
it's the same damn snow.
Oh well. Death'll
be here soon enough.
When he comes for me,
I'll see Ruus again.
[QUENT]
Who are you?
You chugged all of my
restorative potion.
[QUENT]
To me, it was the water of life.
Ah. I'm back from the grave.
[IYEK] I was asked as
a favor to rescue you.
To rescue me?
Yeah. Asked by a wolf.
Yeah right, pal. Not likely.
[IYEK] Why? Don't you
believe in wolves?
[QUENT]
Oh, I believe in 'em all right.
I believe they're
servants of the devil.
[IYEK]
Here's some food.
I'll keep my promise
to help you,
regardless of what
kind of man you are.
Why in the hell
would they want to show
me pity at this point?
[QUENT]
Gimme a freakin' break.
[TSUME]
Why are all these idiots
going soft over
a bunch of women?
We men have our own world.
A world of blood and
grease and gunpowder,
that reeks of sweat!
On second thought, I'll take
the one with the women.