[GUARD A]
This makes six shots.
A rifle was fired
at four young men
accompanying a girl who's
believed to be the target.
It's just like he said
to the Commander.
Those "Forest of Death" rumors.
Do you think they're true?
[GUARD B]
The geomagnetic abnormalities
have been confirmed.
Compasses are useless,
and machines go haywire
the minute you turn 'em on.
[GUARD A]
They say nobody's ever gone in
and made it back
out alive, right?
I wouldn't be surprised
if that place was haunted.
Ha. If you're so
curious, why not go in?
[GUARD C]
Uh.
[chuckles nervously]
Yeah, get real.
[HIGE]
Man, this place is depressing.
I thought forests were supposed
to be more alive, y'know?
It's the Forest of
the Death, remember?
That's the reason the humans
can't follow us in here.
Well, we don't have to rely
on compasses or whatever,
but shouldn't there at
least be some animals?
You know, like a
rabbit or a fox?
Rabbit, huh? In other
words, you're hungry.
Sue me, all right?
[KIBA] We'll probably
come across a town
once we're through this forest.
Just hang in until then.
If we make it out of
here alive, that is.
[TOBOE yelps]
--[crack]
--[gasps]
[screams]
There're plenty of bugs, though.
Thanks a lot, Tsume.
I've never seen
a bug like this.
Here.
Eww.
You're hungry, aren't
ya? Chow down.
Why the hell should I?
'Cause you've got the
strongest stomach, right?
Eat it.
I ain't yer taster!
And how come you're
givin' me orders?
You're not our leader
or anything. Right?!
Hey, I know!
Let's give it to Cheza!
I bet you're hungry, right?
Cheza does not eat bugs.
Well then, what
should we feed her?
This one doesn't eat anything.
Not a thing?
Now that you mention it,
I've never seen her eat.
She drank some
water that one time.
This one drinks and basks.
Basks in what?
But not here...
I get it. Sunlight.
Makes sense. She is a Flower.
[QUENT groaning]
[QUENT] It was just
like I told ya, right?
Four 30-caliber
metal jacket slugs.
It was six.
[COMMANDER] Now, why
don't we try this again,
from the beginning.
Do you always treat
helpful civilians this way?
Who are offer you information?
Of course, a shot of vodka
might make me more cooperative.
I was told you had a dog with
you, so what happened to it?
[QUENT] Ain't there anything
to drink around here?
We found animal bite marks
on the corpses of my dead men.
There weren't any pet dogs in
that town, much less any strays.
[QUENT chuckles]
[QUENT]
Well, shucks, Commander,
I guess they all must've
been killed by wolves.
[growls]
[chuckles]
Yeah, sure it
must've been wolves.
[KIBA]
Let me see it.
[TOBOE]
Okay...
[KIBA]
Well, it doesn't look sprained.
--[crack]
--[TOBO groans]
He can't even handle
this little forest.
Like I always say, ya can't
take city kids to the woods.
Do you think you can walk?
I'm okay. I can
walk just fi--
[HIGE]
Hm?
Cheza.
Uh, Cheza.
[gasps]
Wow, thanks, Cheza.
[HIGE]
Does that feel good?
Mhm. Real good. The pain
is just melting away.
[TOBOE giggling]
[HIGE] Cheza, um...
could you pet me, too?
C'mon, Tsume.
Have Cheza pet you, too.
It feels unbelievable!
[HIGE]
Ah, she smells so good!
[sighs]
Where have you taken me?
Please forgive
my rude behavior.
[DARCIA]
I simply wanted to see you.
Where is Cheza?
It would seem Cheza despises
both me and your people.
What are you after, anyway?
Tell me. Cheza... what is she?
What's her significance?
Lord Orkham is ignorant
of her purpose.
He stole the Flower
Maiden from my clan
solely as a display
of his power.
What do you intend
to do with me?
That depends entirely on you.
This forest ain't so bad,
once ya get used to it.
Nothin' to fight over.
And the best part is
there's no humans around.
We've got it all to ourselves.
Yeah, if we get hungry, there's
plenty of bugs we can eat.
Ha! Fat chance, pal!
Then you'd better not complain
when we don't share
'em with you.
I'll say it again.
Who the hell died and
made you the leader, huh?
Neither one of us
is the leader, Hige.
Ours isn't kind of
pack that has one.
What kind of pack are we, then?
Guys, c'mon, that doesn't
really matter, right?
Hey, I know!
When we all finally
make it outta here,
what's the very first
thing you wanna do?
What do ya think?
Eat as much as I can.
Eat and sleep.
[stomach growling]
Uh. I guess you're right.
[HIGE]
You moron, isn't it obvious?
Cheza!
You must be exhausted.
We'll rest a while.
It is all right,
this one is fine.
[rustling]
[HIGE]
A bird!
Where?
It's the Forest of the Death.
You must be seein' things.
No. I'm sure I heard the
flapping of wings above us.
It was from an owl.
Which means...
...we got meat!
[TSUME]
Hey, Hige! Come back here!
Ugh. Damn it. What an idiot.
Stay here.
Okay.
You must've seen some dead
leaves fallin' or something.
Let's go back.
It doesn't make sense...
I'm absolutely sure I saw it.
[OWL hooting]
[HIGE] See, what'd
I tell ya? It was an owl!
But there isn't enough meat
to split with everybody.
Careful, Hige.
[HIGE]
Huh?
There isn't any scent.
[HIGE]
Hm?
[sniffing]
[TSUME] There's somethin'
suspicious about that owl.
[OWL] An owl that's suspicious?
Wolves that look delicious?
They all wandered in and
got lost as one. Well done!
That thing's screwing with us.
[OWL] Lost as one!
Well done, well done!
Damn it.
[howling]
That howl, is that?
Toboe.
[KIBA]
Cheza!
Hang in there. You can do it!
What's wrong?
[TOBOE]
All of a sudden, she just...
[TSUME]
What? Is that...?
Is she withering?
[KIBA]
She needs water!
Even sunlight will help!
But there isn't any.
The woods are too thick.
And the ground, it's too dry.
We'll never find
any water here.
We have to!
We still have to try.
[TOBOE] Huh. Which way
do you think we should go?
I say to the right.
Hige, do you smell
any water from there?
No, not a drop.
But just standin' here
isn't helping us any.
[OWL] Here isn't helping.
Here isn't helping.
It's an owl.
Damn thing is back.
[OWL] It can't be helped
if there is no light.
It can't be helped
if there is no water.
It can't be helped if
the Flower is withering.
What did you say?
Wait a minute.
That owl probably lives
here in this forest, right?
And if he does...
...don't you think he knows
where we can find water?
[KIBA gasps]
All right, tell us!
What's the closest place
around here that has water?!
Stupid bird! Cut the theatrics
already and spill it!
Do you live here in
this forest or not?
If you do, then tell us!
She has to have water now!
[CHEZA] Kiba? Kiba?
Who are you talking to?
To an owl, Cheza.
[CHEZA]
An owl?
[OWL]
Who?
Come on! Isn't there any
water in this forest?!
[OWL] Go astray,
go astray, my good wolves.
Answers always lie in confusion.
We can't lose him! He's
the only lead we've got!
[OWL] You never find
what you are looking for.
If the searcher were to find
that which is searched for,
it would become a mere object.
[OWL]
Who!
The answer lies
within the darkness.
within confined spaces.
Only those who bravely
enter will be rewarded.
That a riddle?
Birdbrain wants us
to go in the cave.
So does that mean
there's water inside?
How should I know?
Hey, don't go in there!
Are you gonna believe
what some old owl tells you?
This whole thing stinks!
You tell me where we
can find water, then!
Can you do that Hige?!
At this point, we don't
have any other choice.
So much data.
You only know the slightest
fraction about Cheza.
Is what was written in the
Book of the Moon the truth?
Tell me, do you believe
what you've read?
I've seen them.
I've seen wolves.
They were running together
by Cheza's side.
I see.
I'm sure of it now.
They were the same wolves
who turned up in the city.
The same ones who first
appeared when Cheza awakened.
[DARCIA] They will be
the key to Paradise.
To Paradise?
[OWL]
Only those who bravely enter.
Who bravely enter.
We saw this a while ago.
You mean we've been
goin' in circles?
Stupid place is like a maze.
And to make matters worse,
it all looks the same.
[KIBA]
We went left last time.
Damn it all!
Just take it easy, will ya?
Kiba. You're just tired, right?
You want me to carry her?
Why? Can you carry her?
Do you think you can
carry her? Answer me!
[TOBOE]
Well, I...
I'm fine, so walk! We don't
have time to take a rest!
Would you cut the crap?
We can't trust your
nose anymore.
The scent of Flowers
has screwed it up.
My nose is fine!
Kiba, put Cheza down.
Tsume, do you still
not trust her?!
With the way you've been acting,
it's you we can't trust.
[TOBOE]
Huh?
As leader of a pack, you have
to be calm and detached.
And right now,
you don't have that.
It's impossible for someone to
be right all the time, you know.
Stay outta my way.
[growls]
Is that a threat?
--Guys, cut it out!
--[crunch]
[TOBOE]
Huh?
Are... they bones?
Human bones?
I'm not so sure. I think
they're from a bird.
A bird?
[TOBOE] It looks like...
Wait, could this be an owl?
[yelps]
There's a million of 'em!
I knew we shouldn't
have trusted that owl!
[HIGE]
Let's get outta here!
Where can we go?!
[yelps]
Cheza!
[TOBOE]
Get off, stupid bug!
[TSUME]
Kiba!
Up here!
Tsume!
Tsume...
We'll handle it.
Are wolves gonna lose
to a bunch of bugs?
Though I must admit, we both
like to hang around Flowers.
Heh. Nicely said, runt.
Here they come.
--[crunching]
--[snarling]
[CHEZA]
Everyone.
[CHEZA] Wait...
We'll all go... together.
This one can be...
useful, too.
Cheza!
Damn it!
Cheza, no! What're you doing?!
[CHEZA]
That way. Through there!
[KIBA]
Cheza!
No. Wait.
[KIBA]
Cheza.
Don't worry. This one is fine.
Thank goodness.
[CHEZA] This one heard them.
They said they were hungry.
They're plants that
eat bugs, huh?
I guess this means we were
saved by Cheza's friends.
[TOBOE]
Hey, guys!
I see light! It's the way out!
[TOBOE]
There's water!
And check it out,
there's is moonlight, too!
[HIGE]
Water! Yes!
[splashing]
Look, Cheza. There's
your water. Now you can.
This one will be able to
eat and drink all it wants.
Yeah.
[HIGE] Hey, Toboe,
drink up, ya runt!
[TOBOE]
I've had plenty!
[HIGE]
Aw, come on!
[TSUME]
Hige, leave him alone.
[DARCIA] The life of
a Flower is very brief.
[CHER]
Huh?
And Lunar Flowers
are no exception.
Moonlight will give her
strength to survive for now.
However,
after basking in the full moon
only a few more times,
Cheza's life will
come to an end.
[KIBA]
No one really knows
what the future has
in store for them.
If they can't avoid it,
then why do people always
wanna know what it is?
On the night of the full moon,
the path will be revealed.