Ah, man. I sure am hungry.
Yeah, you could say that again.
How long has it been
since we ate anything?
I don't know.
I guess it's been
about three days or so.
[TOBOE] We've gone that
long without eating?
[HIGE]
Yep. Not a bite.
How much longer before
we get any food?
I have no idea. Another
three days, I guess.
Will you two quit your
whining, already?
It's only been
three stupid days.
[TOBOE] Yeah, but if
we hadn't left the city,
we would have something
to eat right now.
[KIBA] We can last a lot longer
if we bask in the moonlight.
I traveled a full month
once when I did that.
Did you say a month?
It should stop
snowing anytime now.
Once it does, and night draws
closer, the moon will be out.
Well, if worse comes to worse,
we can always eat each other.
[HIGE, TOBOE gasp]
We could start with the runt,
since he's gotten so weak.
And of course there's always
little porky over there.
Wait a second! How come
Kiba isn't on the menu?
Because the guy's totally
full of crap that's why.
[TOBOE]
Come on, cut it out!
You don't mean it!
You're just sayin' stuff like
that 'cause you're hungry.
Ah!
[TOBOE]
I wonder where it came from.
I mean it's all
by itself out here.
You' gonna eat that?
Yeah, aren't you gonna?
You know what?
This tastes pretty good.
It's only a little bit
tougher than hamburger.
Hey! Come on, Tsume, have some.
We still have a long
way we have to go.
[TSUME]
Go? Go where, exactly?
To that Paradise place?
Off in the direction
you smell the Flower?
Tsume.
Come on, Kiba, tell us,
what's Paradise really like?
It's an amazing place.
The flowers are always in bloom
and there's food everywhere!
Oh, and there are beautiful
babes all over the place.
You mean it?
Of course there are.
Heh. I hope so, anyway.
You don't know.
[TSUME] Paradise is just a
totally unfounded fairy tale.
And if it isn't,
then it's probably
just some idiot's dream.
So then why the hell'd
you come with us?
[TOBOE] We'll never know
unless we look for it.
How far are you gonna let
this guy string you along?
How far are you gonna follow
this guy in pursuit of a place
that doesn't even
exist to begin with?
That's it. I can't put up
with you losers anymore.
[TOBOE]
Tsume!
Hey, where do you think
you're goin' all by yourself?
To look for Hell I guess.
[KIBA]
Suit yourself.
[TOBOE]
Kiba.
But remember,
that set of rules you have
doesn't apply way out here.
It really pisses me off
when a smug kid like you
has that "know it all"
look on his face
and he's actually clueless.
[TSUME]
Hmph.
Tsume!
Come on, don't leave now. We've
finally made some friends!
[TSUME] Play with your buddies
all you want. I'm outta here.
If ya ask me, the only one who's
acting like a kid around here
is him.
Don't say that. I like
Tsume, he's really nice.
Just wait here.
I'm gonna go get him.
[TOBOE]
Hey! Wait for me, Tsume!
What're you so mad about, huh?
Come on, come back
and join us, okay?
Shut the hell up!
You know it's dangerous
to move around alone.
It doesn't matter, does
it? We're always alone.
But wait I--
Stop bothering me!
And don't follow me.
[TOBOE]
Tsume!
[clink]
[TOBOE]
Tsume!
Hey! Tsume!
[howling]
[TOBOE]
Tsume!
Hey! Tsume!
[explosion]
[gasps]
[HUBB] He came this
close to shooting the guy
right in front of me.
[CHER]
Keep your voice down.
[HUBB]
That man is unbelievable.
He's convinced that
those boys are wolves
and nothing on this earth
is gonna change his mind.
Listen, Hubb.
There's something I need
to you to do for me.
[CHER]
If it's not too much trouble,
could you water the plants in
my apartment while I'm gone?
Gone? What do you mean?
[CHER] I'm... taking
a little vacation.
I'll be gone for a while.
Vacation? Wait a minute,
what's going on?
I thought you said you
were feeling better.
That's why I'm
taking a vacation.
I don't understand,
what about... Uh...
You know. That thing that you've
sacrificed your whole life for?
Including us?
It doesn't really matter
whether I'm here or not.
Nothing's ever going to change.
Certainly not the lab,
or even the world.
What're you saying?
[CHER]
All this work I've been doing,
I mean, seriously,
what's the point?
I feel like everything
around me is an illusion.
I just... don't know
what's real anymore, Hubb.
So much for light conversation.
[HUBB] You know wolves
may actually exist.
But, Hubb.
Listen to me, that dog
we saw was not--
Stop it, Hubb.
Just hear me out. I think there
may be more of them, Cher.
[CHER]
Okay, give it a rest,
I don't wanna think
about it right now.
I'm going.
You're going now? But...
[CHER]
Thanks for dinner.
[HUBB]
Uh.
Oh, Cher, wai-wait a minute!
[TSUME groaning]
Are you okay?
Stay away!
[humming]
We're gonna have to jump.
But...
What the heck is that thing?
How should I know?
[TSUME grunts]
Tsume.
Dammit.
The stench of this place
is startin' to make me sick.
You know, I was thinkin'.
We should go ahead
and ditch that guy.
I mean, it's not like he has to
tag along with us, or anything.
It was happenstance
that threw us together,
and they just ended up
with us, that's all.
The same goes for you.
I don't know. That Tsume
guy's been giving me
a real dangerous vibe
from the start.
[KIBA] He's just difference
from us, that's all.
He always had
someone else to blame.
It's pretty darn lucky,
if you ask me.
Give him a break,
he'll come around.
Okay, so what the hell
is up with you anyway?
I mean, you're always talkin'
like you got an answer
for just about everything.
What happened to you
before all this?
Nothin' much.
Nothin' much at all.
[TOBOE, TSUME yelp]
[screams]
Hey!
Hey, Kiba, do you smell that?
[HIGE]
What's that?
Hm. Maybe there used to be
a military base around here.
[HIGE]
Hey, Kiba! Wait!
[sighs] What a drag.
Whatever.
[groaning]
Stop that! Don't ever touch me.
What's it doing?
It's not after us. Looks
like we gave it the slip.
[TOBOE]
You're covered in scars.
That one. There on your chest.
Man, it's really cool!
[TOBOE] I wonder what
happened to Kiba and Hige.
I bet they're pretty
worried about us by now.
[TSUME]
I don't trust anyone.
And because of that
no one has to trust me.
That way, it keeps
things nice and simple.
I don't care. I still
like you anyway, Tsume.
[clanging]
Ah, damn!
Forget about it, Tsume!
You'll get yourself killed!
Well at least then you'll
finally have something to eat.
Don't be stupid!
I'll act as a decoy
and distract him
so you can get away!
Don't do it!
You can trust me, it's okay.
[howling]
[HIGE]
Tsume!
This way!
Water the plants?
She doesn't have any.
Huh?
[HIGE]
Hey, you okay?
[KIBA]
It's only a scratch.
Yeah, right.
Ever since I met you guys,
nothing but trouble.
I knew it.
Well I wasn't sure,
but I had a feeling that you
guys would come for us.
Well, don't get
too used to it, kid.
[TSUME]
I didn't ask for help.
Why would you do that,
risk your life for me?
And don't try telling me that
it's because we're friends.
That's easy.
It was just instinct.
[HIGE] It's really a drag being
hungry all the time, ya know?
I mean, it's a
crappy way to live.
A man needs adventure
and romance in his life.
And this one man...
who lives for love.