[SHIZUKU]
Okay, if it's not there,
it should definitely
be over here.
[ABENO]
You didn't throw it away?
[SHIZUKU]
No!
C'mon, an inventory list?
Not in a million years!
Probably.
Probably?
If I end up losing
one of Koura's
precious inventory lists,
who knows what she's
gonna do to punish me!
I bet I'll end up getting
mixed in with the ingredients!
Don't worry.
It'll turn up eventually.
Uh... Wait.
Something jog your memory?
Oh, uh...
No, but did Ashiya go somewhere?
He was just in here
a minute ago.
Shizuku, dear?
[SHIZUKU]
Yes, ma'am?
I believe that you're
looking for this?
[SHIZUKU]
Oh, thank goodness!
It was hiding in the kitchen.
Itsuki?
Something the matter?
[ABENO] Forgive me, but I
can't leave the five-year-old
to his own devices.
[SHIZUKU]
Aw, you're taking off?
Sorry, shouldn't be too long.
Ashiya's an idiot.
Wait, seriously?
But, Fuzzy...
What are you even doing here?
[CAPY]
Damn vermin.
You in cahoots with this thief?
He's got absolutely
nothing to do with this!
[CAPY] Well, 'less he wants
to see his buddy get hurt,
he'd best behave.
You're on thin ice as it is.
[ASHIYA]
It's okay. I'll be fine.
Go. Run!
[CAPY growling]
Fuzzy! No!
[CAPY]
Ugh! Get off of me!
[ASHIYA]
Fuzzy!
[CAPY]
Stay right there, ya punk!
[ASHIYA]
Stop it! Let go!
[CAPY] Hardly seems worth
the trouble now, huh?
[ASHIYA]
No.
[CAPY]
What the--?
What are you doing?
[ASHIYA]
It's not.
I understand why you're upset.
But you ignored me.
Nothing I had
to say got through.
All you did was run your big
fat mouth without listening.
You even had the nerve
to pull a knife on me.
You took your anger
out on someone
who was trying to help.
Your actions were indefensible.
You realize that, surely.
[ASHIYA yells]
[ABENO]
A... shi... ya....
Uh-oh.
Um, hey there, Abeno.
Imbecile.
You wandered from the
shop without my leave.
What's going on?
Better yet, what the hell
have you gotten into?
Well, I--!
[ASHIYA]
He's really scary right now.
I'm a dead man.
[ABENO] Ah, perhaps
you imagined I'd smile
and greet you with open arms;
chalk it down to inexperience?
Am I a babysitter?
[CAPY] Wait, what was he
babbling about earlier?
Something about working for
the Mononokean, right?
If that's true, then...
Oh, no!
This angry guy must be...
Calm down, Itsuki!
You can't just start a fight
in the middle of the street
like some kinda thug; you're
the master of the Mononokean!
[ABENO]
Back off!
Let go of me, Shizuku!
Wait, did...
Did she just call him the
"master of the Mononokean?"
I think so, yeah.
What the heck is going on?
Why are you talking
to this yokai ?
And why the hell is
he on the ground?
You've got the wrong idea!
I'm the victim here!
Fuzzy! He's been hurt!
Hey! Don't walk
away from me!
[ASHIYA]
It's okay.
Don't try to move.
Let me see.
That's the yokai
from the other day.
Looks like he's been
hurt pretty badly.
What exactly went down here?
[CAPY]
Uh... Nothing!
It was--!
Can you stand up?
Please, sir.
Whatever mischief my
employee's gotten into
at your expense,
let me put it right.
Hey!
I didn't do anything wrong!
You're a child!
Shut your mouth!
[CAPY]
Uh, are...
Are you really who
they say you are?
The rumored second master?
Yes.
[CAPY]
I don't believe it!
The man who killed
his predecessor,
standing right in front of me!
[ABENO]
A word of advice.
Take the rumors you hear
about me with a grain of salt.
I am simply the current master.
Now, then.
Since my employee
is directly involved
in whatever mishap's
befallen you, I'm responsible.
I'm sorry, but as
there's been violence,
I have to report this
to the authorities.
See, at the end of the day it's
a clear violation of the rules.
With any luck, you'll
get off with a fine, but...
[CAPY]
Wait!
I had nothing to do with this!
I'm just--
I'm just an innocent bystander!
Hey! What are you talking about?
--That's a lie!
--[CAPY] Terribly sorry!
I really must be going!
Whoa! Stop! Get back here!
Ashiya! It can wait!
Right now our priority is
getting back to the Kiyakudo
and treating him!
[ASHIYA]
Yeah, right.
[KOURA] They're certainly
taking their time, aren't they?
What's taking so long?
Surely they've found
Ashiya by now.
[phone ringing]
Huh? Oh, a tadpole line.
Koura here. To whom
am I speaking, please?
[LEGISLATOR]
So formal.
It's just me.
Oh, my! Legislator!
[LEGISLATOR chuckles]
C'mon. Don't do that.
Calling me by my
job title is so cold.
Makes me think you
have ulterior motives.
You know perfectly well
I always have ulterior motives.
The vocal cords
producing that voice
would make an absolutely
splendid medicine.
[LEGISLATOR] I'm sure they
would. Is Shizuku here?
Sorry. Not at
the moment, I'm afraid.
She's out with Itsuki.
[LEGISLATOR]
Itsuki?
He's in the Underworld
right now?
[KOURA] Good help is
so hard to find these days.
Literally in this case,
it seems.
His new whipping boy's
gone missing,
so they're out trying
to rein the lad in.
[LEGISLATOR]
Whipping boy?
What do you mean?
His new employee,
or have you not heard?
[LEGISLATOR]
Ah. I see.
Itsuki's supposed to run
all new hires by me first.
Seems our friend's not
a stickler for protocol.
Do me a favor.
Yes, darling?
[LEGISLATOR] Would you mind
giving him a message for me?
It'd be my pleasure.
Go for it, love.
[LEGISLATOR] The new boy
has to meet with my approval.
That's the way it's always been,
that's the way
it always will be.
I have the final say.
And rules are rules.
Tell Itsuki to bring him
to me without delay.
Thank you.
[ABENO]
I can see your predicament.
Sorry.
It all just
happened so quickly.
[door opens]
Here we are.
All patched up now.
[ASHIYA]
Fuzzy!
So then, he's gonna
be all right, yeah?
Yeah! It's not nearly
as bad as it looks.
With a little rest he should
be as good as new in no time!
That's great news!
You two are a couple
of miracle workers!
Okay, then.
Well, I guess he just
let everybody know
who his favorite is.
Wow. He's such a love bug.
[ASHIYA]
Go on, Abeno.
You can pet him, too,
if you want.
That's not why I'm...!
Oh, forget it.
Does his contact not
affect you anymore?
[ASHIYA]
Whoa. I don't feel like crap!
Oh, my goodness.
I almost forgot.
The Legislator asked me to pass
on a message to you and Shizuku.
The Legislator?
Great. Just what I need.
[SHIZUKU] What does
my brother want this time?
Well, for you,
he says he misses you
and would like a
visit sometime soon.
That poor fellow's
very lonesome.
[SHIZUKU] I was just
over there yesterday!
[ASHIYA]
Okay.
[KOURA]
And for Itsuki...
He expects you to bring
your new employee by
for his approval
as soon as possible.
Something about rules.
He didn't seem too
happy about having to ask.
I wouldn't wait.
What?! You've gotta
be kidding, right?
He's the one who
made it legal for masters
to choose their employees
in the first place!
I'm sorry, darling.
But it's no use
complaining to me.
I just don't understand
why he would change his tune
all of a sudden.
Well, my dear.
I can't say for sure,
but perhaps it's
because you neglected
to tell him you hired someone.
He did seem rather sulky.
Course he did.
Fine.
We have no choice but to go.
[ASHIYA]
Go where, exactly?
Newt Lake. That's where
the Legislator dwells.
All righty, then. Who's he?
And should I be worried?
Worried? Come on!
We're talking about my brother!
[ABENO] He's my superior.
There, I said it.
Seriously?
It's the way of things.
He's one of three
influential figures here.
They essentially
manage the Underworld.
[ASHIYA]
And we're going to see him?
Well that settles it.
What?
I'll give you the medicine
we've made thus far
so you don't go away
empty-handed.
That'd be great.
Oh, hey, and would
you mind throwing in
some of that healing
salve while you're at it?
What would you need it for?
To take care of the hairball.
[ASHIYA]
Really?
Does that mean we're
taking him back with us
to the Mononokean?
Of course.
Somebody has to look after him.
And by somebody,
naturally, I mean you.
[ASHIYA]
Don't worry! I'm all over it!
Aw.
[ABENO]
He really likes you.
Li'l guy must feel super safe
to fall asleep on you like that.
[KOURA]
Here's the medicine.
I'll have the rest made
the next time you visit.
Thank you again.
[ASHIYA] Whatever it is,
that stuff must be important.
Well, good luck
with the Legislator.
See you again real soon!
Sure!
Thanks a lot for
patching up Fuzzy.
[ABENO]
Aside from the Legislator,
there's the Justice
and the Executive.
They're the three big shots
I mentioned earlier.
True to his name, the Legislator
has the power to set rules.
Anyone who breaks
those rules is punished.
[ASHIYA]
Punished in the Underworld?
Sounds terrifying.
It is, or at least
I suppose it would be
if I weren't exempt.
According to the rules, the
master of the Mononokean
is permitted to
act independently.
[ASHIYA] Wait, so they
just let you run around
and do whatever you want?
How does that work?
[ABENO] Shut up,
I'm not a wild animal.
Besides, I'm not above the law.
There is one rule
I have to follow.
Wow. Just one?
[ABENO]
Yes.
"The master must obey any
rule directly imposed on him
by the Legislator."
If I run afoul of that,
I lose my job.
End of story.
[ASHIYA]
Makes sense, I guess.
How much farther?
And shouldn't there be
a path or something?
We're just wading through grass!
How do you know
we're not totally lost?
Quit whining.
We're taking a shortcut.
Stop acting like a baby.
Newt Lake is just up ahead.
And that's where
the Legislator is, right?
You said something about
him "dwelling" there.
Yes.
So what kind of
yokai we dealing with?
He's not dangerous or anything?
[ABENO]
Hmm... Not exactly, no.
Then again, he gambles.
And he's a full-blown
unapologetically
alcoholic pervert.
So a real pillar of society.
Doesn't seem like the kinda guy
I'd want making the rules.
He loves his sister.
[ASHIYA]
Um, let me get this straight:
He's the guy who gets
to decide whether or not
I'm worthy of being
your employee?
[ABENO]
Unfortunately, yes.
[ASHIYA] If he fires me, I'm
gonna have to rethink my life.
[ABENO]
Do what?
Hey, perk up.
I'm not just gonna
let him fire you.
[ASHIYA]
So, like...
You being all mean
is just an act?
You actually like
having me around?
Slow down.
Don't read into things.
You have a debt to pay off.
[ASHIYA]
Oh. Right.
We're here.
[ASHIYA]
Whoa.
This is Newt Lake?
So, you wanted to see me?
[LEGISLATOR]
Itsuki. Glad you could make it.
Finally. I assume this
boy is the new hire?
Well, it's my pleasure to
welcome you to Newt Lake.
[ASHIYA]
Not what I was expecting.
What's the matter, Fuzzy?
[LEGISLATOR] This is what I get
for putting my faith in you.
I realize vetting isn't easy.
But picking someone so weak?
For crying out loud,
one look is all you need.
Consider another line of work.
No offense, but you just
don't have what it takes.
Come on!
You can't just spout
off crap like that!
[LEGISLATOR]
He can't handle the job.
You expect me to candy-coat it?
Moot point either way.
Humans aren't suited
to the life.
[ASHIYA]
He knows I'm human?
[LEGISLATOR]
Am I wrong?
[ASHIYA]
I'm not what I look like!
I'm a yokai !
Really! Um, yeah.
A special humanoid yokai !
[ABENO]
Worst liar ever.
[ASHIYA]
Back me up, please!
Whatever. Fine.
He's a human being.
Are you happy?
What's the deal, Abeno?!
I thought we weren't
supposed to give it away!
Do they know
you're human, too?
Should we let them in
on that little secret?
Keep it down, moron!
[ASHIYA]
I know what this is!
You're abandoning me
to save yourself!
[ABENO]
Will you please shut up?
You're throwing
me under the bus!
I'm not an idiot!
Jerk face! Traitor!
Con artist! Petty tyrant!
Knock it off!
One more word out
of you and that's it!
[laughing]
Besties, huh?
[ASHIYA, ABENO]
Stay out of this!
Your name wouldn't be
Ashiya, by any chance?
Um... Yes, it is.
[ASHIYA]
Wait...
Why is this familiar?
Just so you know,
I had my own reasons
for hiring him.
And besides, you think
I'd take someone on
who couldn't handle it?
If I didn't have full confidence
in him, he wouldn't be here.
[ASHIYA]
Confidence?
Does he really mean that?
Sure, he's a failure
who makes my job harder
more often than not,
and he's supremely irritating.
[ASHIYA]
Thanks for lifting me up.
And if you make a rule
saying I have to fire him,
I won't disobey protocol.
I'm not the type of guy
who likes to rock the boat.
That being said, however...
As long as it's not
an official rule,
then I'm not going to fire him.
Well... Itsuki
has spoken his mind.
What's your opinion
on the matter?
Can a human being do the job?
Can you give yourself
mind, body, and soul
to the service of yokai ?
[ASHIYA]
Mind, body, and soul?
Seems like kind of a tall order.
All for yokai ?
[ASHIYA]
Am I willing to do it?
Serve them?
[ASHIYA]
You're right, Legislator.
I'm human; there's no
getting around that fact.
But what you're asking
makes no sense!
You might as well tell me
that I need to give myself
to humankind.
I wouldn't know what you were
talking about then, either!
Really?
Well? Think about it!
What if you were asked to
devote yourself to humans?
It's a nice concept,
but what does it mean? Right?
Same thing applies if we're
talking about serving yokai ,
doesn't it?
Would you stop?
He's speaking in metaphor.
[LEGISLATOR]
No, no. He has a point.
Why would he consider
serving yokai ?
Clearly the greater good
in regard to his own kind
is beyond him.
Hang on a second.
It's not beyond me.
Just something, I haven't,
um, really considered
the scale of before, you know?
I wanted to help
the yokai I've met
through the Mononokean, on an
individual basis, at least.
But I dunno.
Maybe that means
I have the aptitude
for helping all of them.
How could we ever be sure
if you make him fire me?
Now, Itsuki.
Since Ashiya is human,
I assume you plan on returning
to the mundane world?
[ABENO]
Yeah.
[LEGISLATOR] And of course
you're opening a portal
to do so?
[ABENO] "One may only pass
between the mundane world
and the Underworld using
Underworld portals."
You instated the rule
yourself, I believe.
Right, and it's about
time I instated another,
don't you think?
So, "the master and his
employees are free to pass
between the Underworld
and the mundane world
using the Mononokean."
There you have it.
Your well-being is important.
No use wasting energy
opening portals for Ashiya.
[ASHIYA]
So does that mean...?
[LEGISLATOR] Congratulations
on your new employee.
Nicely done.
Well, that's a relief!
I thought I'd be put to death
if you found out the truth!
[LEGISLATOR]
Excuse me?
Don't be such an idiot.
It's okay if the
Legislator knows.
Oh, gee! Thanks a lot!
Would've been nice if
I'd known that earlier!
I tried to say something,
but you were too busy
calling me names.
The Justice, the
Executive, and I know.
Matter of fact,
even Koura's in on it.
Itsuki being a human
isn't any shock to us.
[ASHIYA]
Even Koura knows about it?
Well, what about Shizuku?
[ABENO]
I haven't told her.
[LEGISLATOR]
The fewer yokai in on it,
the better for
everyone, I think.
We don't want it generally
known, understand?
Things could get
rather complicated.
See to it Itsuki's
secret is safe.
Sure.
Fuzzy?
[ABENO]
What's wrong, hairball?
[LEGISLATOR]
Charming nicknames.
You know, I'm rather curious
about our friend here.
Fuzzy, huh?
I can't help but wonder
who you are.
Oh, uh...
Well he sort of got
hurt on account of us.
So we're taking care of the
li'l guy until he gets better.
So hyper.
[ASHIYA gasps]
Fuzzy, no! I'm so sorry!
Are you okay?
[ABENO] Uh, he's
usually better behaved.
No harm done, really.
He just wanted to request
something while you were here.
Seems he's somewhat
keen on the idea
of coming to
work for you, too.
Uh... Is that okay?
I have no problem with it.
Hired.
That was easy!
Whoa, whoa! I'll hire my own
employees, thank you!
[ASHIYA]
Um... Abeno.
What? I'm doing
you a favor.
Having an actual yokai
around might come in handy.
I'm instating a new rule: Itsuki
has to hire Fuzzy immediately.
Now it's law. So there.
But...
Fine. Whatever.
Welcome to the family, Fuzzy!
Are you excited?
Go ahead, both of you.
Okay.
It was a pleasure meeting you.
Feel free to come and
pay me a visit any time.
I'd love to share a bottle
of saké with you.
I'm too young
to drink, actually.
[LEGISLATOR]
Oh, that's right.
The mundane world has that whole
thing about underage drinking.
I can have some tea.
[ABENO]
Don't take him up on it.
Trust me: he'll talk your
ear off for hours.
[ASHIYA]
Go on, Fuzzy. After you.
[LEGISLATOR]
Itsuki.
[ABENO]
What?
Sorry for hiring the hairball.
I suppose I could've at least
discussed it with you first.
Yeah.
No, really.
I think I understand now.
You rejected all the yokai I
recommended for employment,
so I thought you simply
weren't interested.
You had me convinced
you wanted to go it alone
without having to bother
with employees at all.
Silly me.
The truth is you just
didn't want a yokai .
Well, humans aren't particularly
susceptible to parasite shrubs,
so I guess it makes sense.
Abeno? You're coming, right?
Want me to leave the door open?
[ABENO]
Give me a second.
[LEGISLATOR]
Not to get personal,
but aren't you being
just a smidge uptight?
You're concerned, sure.
But logically, the odds
of it happening again--
[ABENO]
Legislator...
Don't go there.
Move it!
You're in the way!
[ASHIYA] Hey! Why are you
so angry all of a sudden?
Bye! Good to
see you, Legislator.
[LEGISLATOR] Consummately
civilized even when he's angry.
Oh, Abeno.
Such a terrifying
master you are.
[ASHIYA]
Hey, you know what?
Since Fuzzy's with us, we're
now the Mononokean Trio!
[ABENO] Ashiya, call us that
again and I'll punch you.
[ASHIYA laughs]
Come on, it's great!
The Mononokean Trio!
[ABENO]
I warned you.