[OKINA]
Dear, oh, dear.
Dreadfully sorry
for all the trouble.
[ABENO]
Not at all.
[YAHIKO]
Haruitsuki!
[ABENO]
Yeah?
My head is still hurting
from Ashiya's shoe.
Why'd he have to throw it at me?
[ABENO]
Let it go.
He didn't mean to;
he just couldn't see you.
[OKINA]
What?
That's odd. His second
sight isn't back yet?
Tomori assured him it would
return in a matter of days.
It isn't in her nature to have
misled the young man.
I'm certain she told the truth.
Don't concern yourself too much.
Things are bound to work out.
[YAHIKO]
Haruitsuki knows.
He went all the way to the
Underworld to ask her in person.
[ABENO] Shut up. I just
happened to be there, okay?
[OKINA]
May I ask what Tomori said?
Just what I already suspected.
The timeframe varies somewhat
from person to person.
If it takes a while, though,
there might be another
underlying cause.
[OKINA]
Hm.
[ABENO]
She's a little worried for him.
If Ashiya goes much longer
not being able to see yokai ,
he may never get his
second sight back.
[OKINA] Any notion of what the
"underlying cause" could be?
[ABENO] Kind of. More of an
educated guess, really.
[OKINA]
Ah. I thought as much.
Certainly explains how
lively things have been
around the shrine, huh?
[ABENO] If you'll excuse me,
Okina. I should go.
[OKINA]
Yes, of course. And don't worry.
As you say, it's
bound to work out.
I hope so. I'm not sure
what I'll do otherwise.
Yahiko. Ready?
Sure. This should be fun.
Wouldn't hurt if you gave
me a few extra treats
for agreeing to help tomorrow.
Fine. What do you
have a taste for?
[YAHIKO]
Rakugan and dumplings.
Oh, and steamed buns,
and, um, potato chips.
Oh! And you know what
else would be yummy?
[TEACHER A] For this example, we
can use the following formula.
First let's solve for "x."
[ASHIYA]
He's out again.
[TEACHER A]
Ashiya?
[ASHIYA]
Should I be worried?
[TEACHER A]
Ashiya!
Yes, sir?
[TEACHER A] I'd appreciate
it if you paid attention.
Sorry. I just spaced out.
[TEACHER A] Do you need to
go to the nurse's office?
Uh. No, sir!
I'm perfectly fine.
[CLASSMATE A] Uh-oh! The kid
from the nurse's office is back!
[CLASSMATES laughing]
[TEACHER A] All right, people.
That's enough. Settle down.
[FUSSHI]
Our club's out today
so we're stopping by
the convenience store.
You got anything going on?
I can come.
I'm gettin' myself a croquette.
Now that you mention it,
I think I'm gonna grab
myself one too.
Hey there, Zenko,
how's it goin'?
Hanae.
Can you talk for a second?
[ASHIYA]
Sorry. You guys go on ahead.
Sure.
[ASHIYA]
Yahiko?
[ZENKO]
Yeah, he just took off.
He said Abeno needed his
help on a job yesterday
and I haven't seen or
heard from him since.
[ASHIYA] Is he trying to
be the new assistant?
[ZENKO]
Dunno.
But to be honest, it isn't
all that unusual for him
to disappear for a couple
of days now and then.
[ASHIYA]
I hope Fuzzy's okay.
It's just, he and Yahiko
aren't exactly best pals.
Fuzzy's scared of him.
Anyway, no point fretting about
it, right? Not much I can do.
[ASHIYA chuckles]
What is it?
[ZENKO] Nothing. You still
can't see 'em, can you?
It's been so long I'm
wondering if I ever will.
I hate to say it, but maybe
it's time to give up.
[ZENKO]
Oh, that's right!
Before he left, Yahiko said
something about he and Abeno
going to a mountain shrine.
He did, huh?
[ASHIYA]
What for?
[ASHIYA] Get a grip. No use
dwelling on what you can't do.
Move on. Forget about it.
[ANTS chattering]
[ASHIYA]
Huh?
Nice try. Why'd I come here?
Way to take my own advice.
[sighs]
[BIG BOSS SCREE]
Ki, ki, ki.
[ASHIYA] I can tell myself
to forget all I want.
[ASHIYA] It's not like
turning off a light.
[ASHIYA]
I need time.
[sighs]
Snap out of it and
focus already.
[ASHIYA] I wonder... are
Jomatsu and the princess okay?
[rustling]
[sighs]
Just my imagination.
[ASHIYA] Kinda hard to
shake the routine, I guess.
I'm still hyper-alert.
[ASHIYA]
Okay! Time to hit the books!
[ASHIYA] What could it be?
The job they're on.
Must be a big one
if Yahiko's along.
[ASHIYA] Ugh. What the
heck is wrong with me?
The more I try to push it out
of my mind, the more I worry!
Uh, am I crazy, or did
something just brush by?
[laughs]
What is my problem?
Why would I laugh out
loud for no reason?
It was almost like...
Please tell me I've only
lost my second sight
and not my mind!
[ASHIYA] This is it.
What did I expect to find?
This is stupid. Coming here
wasn't gonna change anything.
[ASHIYA]
Abeno? Yahiko?
I wouldn't know if he
was here, would I?
Hey, Abeno! Hello?
Come on, Ashiya,
get it together.
You know they're okay.
You're overthinking this.
Why would they be in danger?
I mean, after all:
Abeno is a pro.
I'll have a look around
just in case, but that's it.
[rustling]
[ASHIYA]
Hm?
Whoa there! Is that a yokai ?
Is my sight back? Have I
returned to normal or what?
Am I ready to go back to work?
[ASHIYA]
This leaf, is it...?
Is that you, Okina?
Hang on a minute!
Did Abeno come by here?
He probably had a fox with him.
Are they inside?
Excuse me. Is anybody in there?
Doesn't look like it.
Okina, where'd you go?
[ASHIYA]
That's...
I knew it looked familiar.
I'd recognize the
Mononokean's crest anywhere.
[gasps]
Got some dirt in my eye.
Uh, okay.
Hey, Okina. Is that you?
Huh? Wait, seriously?
All right, then.
But you, uh, you are
a yokai , right?
Terribly sorry: I can't
see you at the moment.
Bear with me, please. I don't
know what you look like, so...
Calm down.
Nothing to be scared of.
He's a yokai . You've got this.
So, d'you, uh,
d'you invite me here
for something in particular?
I'm guessing you must
need an exorcism.
Oh, I, uh... I'm sorry?
I thought you...
Then why...?
[rustling]
[gasps]
[yelps]
[scuttling]
[squelching]
[clattering]
I'm surrounded. Welp.
Now I'm scared. What do I do?
[ASHIYA]
Ugh. I hate this.
It feels like... I dunno... like
I'm in a real-live horror movie.
Working for the Mononokean
desensitized me.
After a while, I let my
guard down around yokai .
Now that I can't see them?
Makes perfect sense Abeno
wouldn't want me around.
He had to draw
the line somewhere.
This freaked out,
I'm a liability.
Still, though, he could've been
nicer about it. I'm on his side.
I just... I just lashed out
at being called dead weight.
Look at me. What am I doing?
I'm petrified.
What if this thing's
not even a yokai ?
There's no way to tell.
Stop it. You're only
making this worse.
Pull yourself together.
I mean it!
You're useless enough
without being scared!
[ASHIYA]
I can't see them.
I can't hear them,
but they're definitely here.
What the--? What was that?
[ASHIYA] I think I can actually
feel them, staring at me.
That's weird. It's
not hostile, though.
Except, how can I be sure?
If I can't see them how can
I read their intentions?
I don't know. I swear
I feel kindness.
As if they're all... smiling.
[thud]
[gasps]
[ASHIYA screams]
[YAHIKO]
Come on, don't throw it away!
[ABENO]
Where'd you get a skull?
[YAHIKO] I found it in the
mountains! Neat, huh?
[ABENO]
Get rid of it.
[YAHIKO]
Aww!
Look at that. How long
you s'pose he'll be out?
Ki. Who'd have thought
the boy would faint?
[NOBOU] Perhaps we should splash
some cold water on his face?
Huh, I'm not sure what
we should do honestly.
Princess Anmo?
Again?!
[MITSUCHIGURA]
I say wake him.
Would you care to do
the honors for us?
[ASHIYA]
Fuzzy.
[ABENO]
Will you get up?
[ASHIYA gasps]
It's Big Boss Scree!
And Mitsuchigura and Manjirou!
And Spiny! And Nobu!
And Princess Anmo!
I don't believe it!
Oh, hey, Abeno. How're you?
[BIG BOSS SCREE]
Ki, ki, ki.
He gathered us here to help
restore your ability
to see yokai .
He gathered you?
[NOBOU] But of course! That's
what friends do, is it not?
He summoned us
and we came running
without a second thought.
[ASHIYA]
You... helped me?
Don't get the wrong
idea, hot shot.
I was already in
the neighborhood
and thought I'd come
along for the ride.
Uh, I had a gift to drop
off at the Mononokean.
[laughs]
[MITSUCHIGURA]
You seem a lot better now!
[laughing]
Fuzzy! I thought I'd
never see you again!
I missed you so much,
and here you are!
Took you long enough
to acknowledge him.
[YAHIKO]
Wow! That was fun!
[OKINA chuckles]
You were just about to start
bawling like a little baby!
Huh?
Wait, so you were the
one holding the skull?
It's not cool to scare people!
Me scaring you is what brought
you back to normal, jerk!
Oh, and you're welcome,
by the way!
[ASHIYA]
What?
[ABENO] I might've told him
to lay it on a little thick.
Um, alrighty, then.
Not to be rude, but what
in the world is going on?
Gimme a break.
You've got your sight back,
what does it matter?
Don't get me wrong, I'm
ecstatic, it's just, y'know...
I'm just curious what
everyone's doing here.
What's different?
Why can I see them now?
Explain it to me! Please!
Shut up. You're so annoying!
[ABENO sighs]
It's not rocket science, okay?
Think back to what triggered
your ability in the first place.
[ASHIYA]
Okay.
The first yokai I saw was Fuzzy.
He was just lying
on the sidewalk.
[ABENO] Okay, and what was
going through your head?
[ASHIYA]
I don't remember.
No, wait, I was thinking about
what high school would be like.
Yeah, I figured it had to
be something lame as hell.
[ASHIYA]
Hey! It wasn't lame!
Look, thing is:
The catalyst wasn't you, okay?
It was you encountering Fuzzy.
Fuzzy granted me second sight?
Not quite, no.
The way you reacted to him
awoke a predisposition.
Essentially you
two "resonated."
You mean, like empathy?
I knew I had to do something
that would take you back,
put you in a receptive
state of mind.
Didn't take much.
[ABENO] Besides, I had help.
These yokai all have a special
place for you in their hearts.
[MITSUCHIGURA] Each and every
one of us stood by your side
throughout this whole ordeal,
praying for your
vision to return.
Wait, so, everything
these past few days...?
Happened for a reason.
Even without second sight,
you could tell they were there.
Your weird devotion to them
meant you only needed a jolt.
You don't have to
say it like that.
If I'm weird, what're you?
[ABENO]
Sorry for all the trouble.
Thank you very much.
[ABENO] What're you
waiting for? Say thanks.
They came all the way from
the Underworld for you.
Show some gratitude.
Aw, you guys!
I really owe you one!
[BIG BOSS SCREE]
Ki, ki, ki. Our pleasure.
[MANJIRO]
Yeah, whatever.
See you around, kid.
[ASHIYA]
Definitely.
Come pay us a visit in
the Underworld someday.
[ASHIYA]
Of course!
[NOBOU] The bonds of friendship
we've forged here are eternal.
[ASHIYA]
Yeah, they are. You're right.
Thank you. Thank you all.
[MITSUCHIGURA]
Of course.
Though when all
is said and done,
we're not the ones you
ought to be thanking.
Abeno, my friend,
if you would be so kind...
[ABENO]
Sure.
[ASHIYA chuckles]
[ASHIYA] Well, that's it.
We've sent them on their way.
[ASHIYA gasps]
Wait a minute, I-- Abeno!
[ABENO]
Hm?
Oh no. I'm pretty sure
my vision went up a level!
I can't just see yokai .
I can see ghosts!
[ABENO]
What?
[ASHIYA] I saw a hand reach out
and grab me through the wall!
It nearly ripped my sweater!
[ABENO]
Oh. That.
Another gig? What the--?
[ASHIYA screams]
[ABENO]
Huh? Ashiya?
[ABENO] So, yeah, your vision
wasn't totally back yet.
The hand you saw was mine.
Ugh! Well it scared
the crap out of me!
[OKINA] I took it upon myself
to call on Abeno here
because you appeared
to be looking for him.
Forgive me for startling you.
On that subject, why did you
come here? Nobody asked you to.
Well, you just, um,
you weren't in class
and I thought maybe...
Look, I was worried, all right?
I know what you're gonna say.
"Use your head. What
good could you've done me?"
[OKINA]
All the same,
we're pleased your ability
to see us has returned.
Don't you agree, Abeno?
Yes.
[YAHIKO] Would've been
awful if it hadn't!
Especially after going
to all the trouble
of getting everyone from
the Underworld to--
[ABENO] Shut up.
Throw away that damn skull.
[YAHIKO]
Haruitsuki, what was that for?
[ABENO]
Just do as I say.
[YAHIKO]
But I wanna show it to Zenko!
[ABENO] You don't just bring
a skull into a temple.
[YAHIKO] Why not?
I'll put it back afterwards!
[ASHIYA]
What?
[YAHIKO]
Haruitsuki.
You arranged this whole thing!
It was your idea!
You even went to the Underworld
just to bring them all here!
And you wanted me
to think I was fired!
Thanks a lot, Okina.
[OKINA chuckles]
I'm really sorry.
If I'd had any idea I wouldn't
have thrown my shoe at you.
Hope it didn't
clock ya too hard.
[YAHIKO]
I'm the one you hit!
[ASHIYA]
Seriously?
Uh-huh. Stupid thing got
me right on the forehead.
[ASHIYA]
You were on the roof? My bad!
The price of forgiveness
is ten dumplings.
[ASHIYA]
Um, glazed or red bean?
Better do both kinds.
[ABENO]
I'll take care of it.
It really oughta be me.
I'll go to the convenience
store tomorrow.
[ABENO]
Ashiya.
[ASHIYA]
Yeah?
[ABENO] Sorry for being so rude
to you through all this.
Forgive me.
If you would like to,
I'd be happy to have
you back on the job.
Are you willing to come
work for me again?
I could use the help.
[ASHIYA]
Huh?!
Why are you bowing?!
It's awkward!
What? It's customary,
you idiot. So?
[ASHIYA]
Huh? Oh.
Yes!
Absolutely.
Uh, I mean, I promise
to do my absolute best!
You won't be disappointed!
[ABENO]
Now it's awkward.
[ASHIYA laughing]
Don't do that,
Fuzzy. It tickles!
[ABENO]
Your absolute best, huh?
[ASHIYA]
Stop!
[ABENO]
What a terrifying prospect.
[ASHIYA] Huh? Really?
Fuzzy never left my side?
[ABENO]
Come rain or shine.
I let him be, to avoid
the separation anxiety.
[ASHIYA] I'm sorry
I didn't see you, buddy.
It must've been lonely.
What'cha tryin' to say?
[ABENO] Don't use speech
bubbles to be cute.
[ASHIYA "I guess I'll
play ball with you."
[ASHIYA]
Not a problem, li'l guy!
Thanks for translating.
Didn't know you could do that.
[ASHIYA]
C'mon, let's go!
[ABENO]
Guessing?
You're both yokai .
It wasn't a shot in the dark.
[ASHIYA]
All right, you ready?
Heads up!
Nice catch!
[ABENO]
You know,
I used to not be tall
enough to ring this bell.
I was determined to
make it ring, though.
I had Aoi lift me up
so I could reach.
Must make you uneasy
the master's human now.
Especially since my
assistant is, too, right?
[gasps]
[ABENO] It's hard for people
and yokai to coexist.
Lot of variables have to
be in perfect balance.
Humans have their strengths,
but we're still mortal.
Before you know it,
we're out of the picture.
[ABENO]
He'll realize that eventually.
[ABENO] What's your take?
Is he worth it?
Yokai employees have
a longer shelf life.
If you want me to
reconsider, I will.
Diplomatic.
[ABENO]
Me, too. I guess.
We're out of the
woods for now, sure.
But I'm thinking about all
the yokai willing to help us.
And the fact it only
took one to fix him.
Seems a little worrisome,
is all. Think about it.
How attached does the hairball
have to be to manage that?
What do you mean?
[ABENO]
Yeah. I know.
Come on, Fuzzy, you gotta
throw it back, all right?
[ASHIYA laughs]
Aw, buddy.
[ASHIYA laughing]
[FUZZY]
Thank you.
[ASHIYA]
You are so freakin' adorable!
[ASHIYA laughing]
[ASHIYA]
Uhh...
Abeno!
[ABENO]
Huh?
[ASHIYA] Um, can Fuzzy
stay at my house tonight?
[ABENO]
What?
[ABENO sighs]
[ABENO]
Yeah. Sure.