It's been a while.
Or has it?
Rather hard to believe you came
here without being summoned.
This must be
extremely important.
It's just some housekeeping.
I thought you should know...
that I released my employee.
[LEGISLATOR]
Hmm...
As the master, you are free
to terminate whomever.
Just the same as when you made
the choice to hire the boy.
[ABENO] But you were
upset that I'd hired him
without informing you before,
so I'm keeping you in the loop.
After all, isn't that
what I should be doing?
Should be doing?
Hmm...
Ah, come now.
It's not as though
you're especially known
for your adherence to protocol.
[grumbles]
Sorry for bothering you.
Can't I hear the
rest of the story?
There has to be more to it.
At the very least,
the reason he was let go.
He's lost his ability
to see yokai .
So say the rumors.
[ABENO]
Yes.
And that's all?
[ABENO]
That's reason enough for me.
If he can't see or hear them,
he can't effectively
help the Mononokean
complete the jobs we take.
We need someone who can.
Yes, but I've also heard
that he temporarily
lent his sight
to a yokai who was in need.
So your decision to fire him
seems a bit rash in my opinion.
What was supposed
to last a few days
has turned into a week now.
The work coming in hasn't slowed
down since that happened.
I simply don't have
the time to wait.
"As long as it's
not an official rule,
I'm not going to fire him."
Does that sound at all familiar?
If I recall, you said that
last time we spoke face to face.
The situation has changed.
Itsuki.
Do you regret your decision?
Huh?
Do you regret hiring him?
[gasps]
[LEGISLATOR] Now you can put
all those doubts to rest.
Is that not what
you were thinking?
Not exactly.
He's too emotionally
invested in yokai .
And it got in the
way of his duties.
I know from experience the
mistakes that can lead to,
so I took action before
things got worse.
[LEGISLATOR]
So it's in his best interest
if he doesn't regain the
ability to perceive yokai .
I understand why
you would relate
the struggle he's going
through to your own.
You don't want him
to have to endure
the hardships
you've gone through.
[grumbles]
Ah.
I honestly had no idea you cared
for your "employee" so deeply.
Eh? Uh?
Cut it out.
I agree that you have
every right to let him go.
But have you even
considered the argument
that he has every right to stay?
How did he take it?
Did he accept your choice
without argument?
Or did he fight back?
[ABENO]
Doesn't matter if he accepts it.
I'm the master and I
did what I had to do.
I have to ask.
Does Ashiya come
from a large family?
Huh?
All he's really said about them
is his mom runs a flower shop,
and that his sister stays
out partying all night.
[LEGISLATOR]
And his father?
Actually, no mention of him.
Are you trying to make a point?
I just find it interesting
that he's a human named Ashiya
who happens to possess
the ability to see yokai .
Did that have nothing
to do with his hiring?
Maybe you should exercise
a little patience with him.
[ABENO] Well, he doesn't
have the ability anymore.
And that gets in the way
of exorcising yokai .
It is my decision as the master.
[phone ringing]
[LEGISLATOR]
Hm?
Hello?
[SHIZUKU]
Brother!
Greetings, Shizuku.
Are you calling to tell me
you're coming home?
[SHIZUKU] No! I was trying
to get a hold of Itsuki.
Is he still there?
He is. Want to speak with him?
[ASHIYA] He didn't come
to school again today.
Is he dealing with
a difficult job?
Maybe with a
really scary yokai .
Whoa, calm down!
Uh. Sorry.
So did you remember
to bring your camera?
Yeah, of course.
I found an old one
we had at home.
That should do the trick.
Are you gonna join
the photography club?
I don't know, but I'm gonna
check it out at least.
[SAGA]
Oh, cool.
[FUSSHI]
Mh-hm.
--[CAT meows]
--[FUSSHI yelps]
Ah, flower pic. I'm glad to
see you're gettin' into it.
Yeah, guess I am.
You've got a natural
eye for framing, man.
I think you should take some
more pictures on the way home
and see if you find something
you've never noticed before.
[ASHIYA] I've only taken
souvenir pictures,
but I'm really starting
to like photography.
Wish I could get
some pics of yokai .
[sighs]
[ASHIYA yelps]
[ASHIYA]
You startled me.
So what's the deal with
the camera? Photography club?
I wasn't really
thinking about it,
but I could totally
see myself joining.
Why? Did you quit your job?
I didn't exactly "quit."
Abeno fired me.
Because you can't see
any yokai anymore?
I see. Yahiko told you about it.
[ZENKO]
Mh-hm.
And I thought of
something you could try.
Well, what's your idea?
I used to not be
able to see them,
but I could after Yahiko bit me.
So there's no reason why that
wouldn't work for you, right?
That's a great idea!
Yeah! Let's go back to your
place right now and try it out!
It's just me.
[ASHIYA] I'm staring
to rethink this idea.
Coming home with Zenko
means I have to see her dad.
Zenko. You're awfully
late coming home.
[ASHIYA]
He was waiting on her?!
It's you.
[ASHIYA]
Ah! Sorry!
I have a perfectly good
reason for being here, sir!
[ZENKO'S DAD]
I'm glad to see you again.
Come in, make yourself at home.
Uh, sir. I'm awfully sorry for
coming to your home so late.
[ZENKO'S DAD] I was just
thinking about asking Zenko
to invite you over.
Oh. You were?
I was.
I have been considering
accepting exorcism requests
at the temple.
Huh?
This is no mere coincidence,
you just showing up
when I had that idea.
It's because you're
psychic, aren't you?
Ha! And it seems
you've read my mind.
I didn't! I can't
read anyone's mind.
[ZENKO'S DAD] Now I haven't
gotten any requests yet,
but when I do, you'll be the
first one to know, Ashida.
It's Ashiya, sir.
And it wouldn't do you
any good to count on me.
[ZENKO'S DAD]
Oh, right.
See?
I even had some postcards made
so I could start spreading
the word about it.
[ASHIYA] "Parishioners troubled
by hauntings, curses,
and all other manner of
supernatural phenomena,
we are now open
for consultations.
This temple is partnered
with a talented psychic."
[yelps]
Sorry, but you've got
the wrong idea about me.
I'm telling you, I am not
a psychic. I see yokai .
Uh.
[ASHIYA] Actually, I guess I
should say I used to see yokai .
Don't you worry.
I promise I'll pay you
a decent wage for it.
Yeah! That's not the
problem here! My point is--
Hey, Dad?
[ASHIYA] Whew! I'm saved
from this living hell!
Although it's kinda strange
to say that about a priest.
[ZENKO]
That's enough.
Hanae came over here because
we have something to talk about.
And what do you
two have to discuss?
[ASHIYA]
Uh! A priest from hell!
[ZENKO]
C'mon, let's go.
Hey, hold on Masuda!
You better not get any weird
ideas about my daughter!
My name's Ashiya.
And speaking of weird,
that wasn't even close.
If you don't stop being
rude to my friends,
I'm gonna tell Mom about it.
What?! No!
I'm just worried about my
little baby girl, is all!
Don't worry, and I'm not
a baby. Just try to relax.
She's right, there is
nothing to worry about.
If someone hires us
for an exorcism,
I'll have him come
back over to help.
[ZENKO'S DAD]
You will?!
[ASHIYA]
Uh.
'Kay, go ahead and
put out your arm.
Is Yahiko around or something?
[ZENKO]
Mh-hm.
He's right behind me.
Why do I have to help this jerk?
I haven't forgiven him for
hitting me with his shoe.
[ZENKO]
Just bite him would you?
I'll give you more
candy if you do.
Aww!
Okay, ten pieces of Rakugan.
It's a deal.
All right then!
That works for me!
Well, there you go.
The bite. Did it work?
Thanks for trying.
I'm sorry.
I thought that would do it.
[SHIZUKU]
Hey! Itsuki!
Something wrong?
I was afraid you'd left already.
I was just on my way out.
What's up? What do
you need from me?
[SHIZUKU]
There's someone at the shop.
He's asking to meet with you.
Why would somebody be
asking for me at Kiyakudo?
[SHIZUKU] You'll understand
when you see him.
[chuckles]
I found Itsuki!
Lovely.
[BIG BOSS SCREE]
Ki, ki, ki. Hello, Abeno.
What a nice surprise.
I wanted to thank you
again for your help.
I hope that you're
feeling better.
[BIG BOSS SCREE]
Ki, ki.
Thanks to you and
these lovely creatures,
my pain has nearly subsided.
We're more than happy to help!
That is why we're here!
[ANTS chattering]
[BIG BOSS SCREE]
Ki, ki.
Yes, I'll tell him.
The little ones want
to say thanks as well.
Yes, of course.
Did Ashiya not come
here with you today?
No.
[BIG BOSS SCREE]
Ki, ki, ki.
Now isn't that a shame?
We wanted to express our true
appreciation and gratitude
to both of you for
all that you've done.
If it weren't for your help,
well, I wouldn't be
here with my children.
I owe the both of you my life.
No. It was actually
Ashiya who saved you.
I don't deserve the credit.
[BIG BOSS SCREE gasps]
[chuckles]
I'm so happy that we
could catch you in time.
Big Boss came here right
after you left the shop.
So I called my big brother
as soon as I could.
[BIG BOSS SCREE]
Ki, ki.
And thank you for that, miss.
Not a problem, sir.
You're a regular, after all!
You're so sweet.
Feel free to take the
rest of the day off.
Seriously?
[KOURA] You have been working
a lot of overtime lately.
And the legislator will
be glad to see you.
Thank you! I'll see
ya later, Itsuki!
Yeah. See ya.
Hopefully, you can bring
Ashiya along with you next time.
I'll think about it.
[SHIZUKU laughing]
Well, Itsuki?
What?
It's just my intuition,
but something happened
with Ashiya, yes?
Huh?
[KOURA] You can't hide it.
Your face gives it all away.
[ABENO gasps]
[KOURA]
I'm joking.
Now I see.
So that's why you sent Shizuku
home all of a sudden, isn't it?
Considering the she
doesn't even know
both you boys are human,
I thought it best to
discuss this without her.
[ABENO sighs]
I honestly wasn't trying to
hide this from you, but...
He can't see yokai anymore?
[BIG BOSS SCREE]
Ki, ki.
Isn't there some kind
of pill he can take?
Unfortunately, human
medicine is well beyond
my area of expertise.
I may be wrong, but he couldn't
always see yokai , correct?
He only gained the
ability to see them
after the hairball
possessed him.
But you're right, before that
he couldn't see them at all.
So there was something
that triggered it?
[BIG BOSS SCREE]
Ki, ki.
Why don't you look
for this Tomori
and find out what
she has to say?
That is an excellent idea,
but since she's new
to the Underworld,
she may be hard to find.
The legislator may
be able to find her,
but he's always so busy,
I'd hate to bother him.
[ABENO] There's no need
to go that far with it.
[KOURA, BIG BOSS SCREE]
Huh?
Ashiya's no longer my employee.
That means he has nothing to do
with the Mononokean or yokai .
[BIG BOSS SCREE]
Ki, ki, ki.
Then I'll go and look
for Tomori myself.
I've got the little
ones with me.
Splitting up will
make it easier.
You don't have to.
[BIG BOSS SCREE]
Ki, ki.
Just don't expect a
miracle from us, okay?
I can't ask you all to go out
of your way just to help me.
Like I said, he doesn't
even work for me anymore.
[ALL chattering]
Itsuki. You should
accept their help.
It's very clear that
they'd be happy to do it.
[ABENO]
Then I accept your offer.
[BIG BOSS SCREE]
Ki, ki, ki.
Abeno. Please wait
here until we return.
I would hate to miss you again.
[KOURA chuckles]
It warms my heart to see
they love Ashiya, too.
[ABENO]
Huh?
I'm extremely fond
of him, myself.
He's just so adorable.
Know her?
She was exorcised
by the Mononokean
a little over a week ago.
The Mononokean sent her?
Ki, ki. Is that so?
[NOBOU] Yes, indeed.
I know her quite well, in fact.
We are both recent transplants
from the Mundane World, you see.
So we had a lotta
things to talk about.
I can introduce you
to her if you'd like.
What is it exactly that
you want from her?
[KOURA] Standing there brooding
won't help, you know?
So what's troubling you?
[ABENO]
My job is to help yokai .
Me asking for their help...
is just pathetic.
[KOURA]  I'm sorry, love,
but you're wrong.
Although that is your
basic job description,
they specifically asked to help.
Because of what you and
Ashiya did for them, right?
But I've already fired Ashiya,
so even if we do find Tomori...
Come now.
Surely you'll agree that this
is an incredible situation.
Yokai helping a human?
[ANTS screeching]
[BOTH gasp]
Does all the screeching mean
they were able to locate her,
or that they weren't?
How would I know?!
[BIG BOSS SCREE]
Ki, ki.
Calm down, little ones.
Good news, Abeno.
Ki, ki. We have found Tomori!
[NOBOU]
Good to see you again!
[ABENO]
Nobou!
[NOBOU] They explained the
situation with Ashiya to me.
After hearing of his troubles,
I couldn't just stand idly by
and not do everything
in my power to help!
[MANJIRO]
Hey!
I heard that Ashiya is
in some kinda trouble!
There's a rumor going around
that he can't see us anymore.
Is that really true?
Yes, that is true.
That's horrible news.
Because if he hadn't seen
me in the first place,
I may never've been able to
fly with my dear princess again.
Hey! Princess!
What is all this?
[MITSUCHIGURA] I recall that
I'd said Ashiya was dangerous.
Oh, Mitsuchigura?
[MITSUCHIGURA]
Upon further reflection,
I realize now that my fears
were completely baseless.
In fact, we've all come together
due to our shared concern
and admiration for him.
You see?
He may be a human,
but he's beloved by yokai .
Sounds like someone else I know.
[ABENO]
I'm going to talk to Tomori.
Hello? Who is that?
[ABENO]
I'm sorry for dropping by
unannounced like this, Tomori.
Really?
'Fraid so. Ashiya still
hasn't regained his ability.
So, if you don't mind,
I wanted to hear some
of your thoughts on this.
In the past, those who
had lent me their vision
had theirs restored in no
more than two or three days.
[ABENO] Yes, that's exactly
what Okina told me.
If I knew this would happen,
I would have never accepted
Ashiya's generous offer
in the first place.
But I wonder...
Yes, what is it?
There may be another
factor in play.
Some reason why it's taking
so long for him in particular.
Oh yeah? What?
I can sense in him some
extremely powerful feelings
regarding we yokai as a whole.
And because his willingness
to help me was so strong,
it's very possible that
he's still subconsciously
holding on to that feeling.
That he's still willing
his vision away somehow.
That does seem likely.
[TOMORI]
However, I'm beginning to fear
that if Ashiya's condition
persists for much longer,
it may mean that he
will permanently lose
his ability to see
or hear yokai .
[ABENO gasps]
I'm very worried
about that, in fact.
[ABENO]
So am I.
Ashiya wasn't able to perceive
yokai until fairly recently,
so maybe he'll lose
it just as quickly.
It just breaks my heart.
And I can't help but feel
responsible for this situation.
I didn't consider any long
lasting results it may have.
If it were possible, I would
gladly give him my own eyes
in the hopes it could make up
for my selfishness, truly.
[ABENO]
It's not your fault.
[TOMORI gasps]
You don't have to carry this
kind of guilt on your back.
I feel so bad.
I had the power to stop him,
but I chose not to.
But still...
Please try not to worry.
I will do my best to make things
right. Help him see again.
And restore your peace of mind.
Besides, it seems the
Mononokean still needs him.
[ABENO] Well, I told her I'd do
it, so I gotta figure out how.
[ABENO]
Mononokean, come.
Something in his subconscious?
[gasps]
[ABENO]
Hate to do this, Ashiya.
I'm not ready to
head back just yet.
Sorry for coming over so late.
So has Abeno
been back to school?
No, he must be on a
pretty serious job.
[chuckles]
But I guess that's none
of my business, ya know?
There has to be some kind
of way you can see again.
Who knows, it may just
come back tomorrow.
[ASHIYA]
Hm. Maybe.
Thanks, Zenko. Goodnight.
[YAHIKO]
Why didn't you tell him?
Hush.
Come on, it's not like
he can hear me anyway.
[YAHIKO]  I mean, he doesn't
even know Fuzzy is with him.
[ASHIYA]
Hey, Abeno!
[ABENO]
What?
[ASHIYA] I know we've been
through a lot of stuff.
I can hardly believe it!
Like, so much has
happened so quickly!
[ABENO]
Yeah, what's your point?
[ASHIYA] I just hope
that you'll stick with me!
'Cause I know I'm gonna need
your help for a long, long time!
[ABENO]
Then stop being so annoying!