[YAHIKO]
This is so fun!
Let's play some more!
We can just keep on
playing all day and night!
Right, Haruitsuki?
Hey, Yahiko.
Yeah? What is it?
[ABENO] Wouldn't you rather go
to the Underworld instead?
There would be a whole lot
more people to play with there.
You'd be happier.
You could play as
much as you wanted.
[YAHIKO] Are you saying that
you want me to go away?
Well?
Do you not want to
play with me anymore?
I still do.
That's great!
Then let's keep on playing
and playing forever!
We'll play hide and seek!
Is it true that you wanted
to succeed Aoi so badly...
...you killed for the job?
Hey. Zenko.
Are you okay?
[ASHIYA]
This is a lot like how I felt
when I was being possessed.
[YAHIKO] You didn't want
to be the servant anymore.
No. You wanted to be
the master of it all.
You wanted the fear
and respect of the yokai .
And you wanted all the
money that came with it.
[ABENO]
Are you jealous?
It's true.
The master of the Mononokean
isn't like anyone else.
And there are a lot of yokai
who would give anything
to have the status and power
that this position holds.
Sure.
But if you ask me,
as far as I'm concerned,
those things are
more of a burden.
Besides.
I killed Aoi to become
the new master, right?
To satisfy my greed.
[ABENO] So that's
what they say about me.
[YAHIKO grunts]
If Aoi had ever heard
a rumor like that one,
they'd have died
from laughter instead.
Listen to me.
I didn't kill the old master.
Got it?
I wouldn't have ever
wished for them to go away.
Never for a damned second.
Zenko! Thank goodness!
You're back. And you're alive!
I am. Was I dead?
[ASHIYA]
Uh... You're alive now!
Haruitsuki. You know...
When I first started
hearing those rumors,
I didn't really believe
that they were true.
Not until I saw you again.
Oh, yeah?
Well, you had just
gotten so much taller,
and you were way more mature
than you were the last time.
It looked like you'd become a
different person altogether.
I wasn't sure if
you were still you.
So I felt like I had to make
completely sure for myself.
But after playing around
with you again today,
I found out you're the same
Haruitsuki I knew back then.
There's no doubt about it.
All those rumors aren't true.
Okay.
But what did you
plan on doing to me
if you found out
that they were true?
Huh...
I guess it would
depend on how I felt.
[ASHIYA]
Zenko, can you stand up?
Yes.
And what about your left arm?
Does it still hurt?
[ZENKO]
Mm-hmm.
Yahiko.
Yes? What?
[ABENO] Over the years,
I've gotten used to dealing
with yokai like you.
So I'll get over this
pretty quickly.
But I'm weird like that.
What do you mean?
[ABENO]
She won't.
You're gonna remove
that thing from her arm.
But it'll take a hell
of a lot more than that
to make it up to her.
Oh, wow. It disappeared.
Just gone.
Not even a trace.
That's great!
Go on.
[YAHIKO]
Yes. Okay.
I'm doing it.
[YAHIKO]
Uh... Miss? Miss Zenko.
I'm very sorry for all
the trouble I put you through,
and for the bite and stuff,
and I take full responsibility.
I'll never do
anything like it again.
Not to you, or to anybody else.
[YAHIKO] If it would
make you feel any better,
you can uh...
Boil me in a pot. Uh...
It's "roast me alive
or whatever you please!"
So start the whole thing over.
Please don't. It's okay.
She said that
everything is okay again!
You weren't sincere at all.
Do it over!
You sure are scarier
than you used to be.
I'm very sorry...
No, that's enough.
You don't have to apologize.
But I would appreciate a favor.
What is it?
For one month,
I'll need you to help
around the temple.
I'd help you take care of it?
[ZENKO]
Mm-hmm.
Hold on a sec, Zenko!
Do you really want Yahiko to
hang around for that long?
Yeah. Can I not?
Well, uh...
It's not really
that you "can't."
Yahiko.
Yeah?
Do you remember eight years ago?
I told you the
Underworld has more people
for you to play with.
Consider that.
And tell me what you wanna do.
[YAHIKO] Are you saying that
you want me to go away?
You're probably mad
that I doubted you.
So, do you not want
to play anymore?
I'll play longer.
That's great to hear!
In that case, instead of
going to the Underworld.
I'll help around the
temple for a whole year!
Whoa! Is that
even allowed, Abeno?
I'd only said a month, but can
he really stay an entire year?
[ABENO]
Just behave yourself.
[YAHIKO]
I will!
[ASHIYA sighs] Well, that was
interesting and everything,
but I'm glad it's over.
Hey. This is
where I met Fuzzy.
It was right in this
very same spot.
What the--?
A bird?
No. Doesn't look right.
Is it real?
[ASHIYA] Wait.
This is way too familiar.
Same spot.
Weird looking thing
on the ground.
[ASHIYA]
I knew it!
Hang on.
You made eye contact.
So you can see me.
[ASHIYA]
I stepped on another yokai ?
Hey, you!
[ASHIYA gasps]
Tell me.
Do you happen to know where
I can find the Mononokean?
[ASHIYA]
Huh?
The princess and I
need to go there!
[ASHIYA]
He's looking for the Mononokean?
We need to be
exorcised or we...
Hey, are you okay?
I... need... water.
Princess!
[ASHIYA gasps]
I'm awake! I'm awake!
I'm sorry.
I guess I dozed off.
[JOMATSU]
Hold on. Where am I?
[gasps]
A human?
Why did you bring me here?
Did you forget?
I picked you up
after you'd collapsed.
You're human.
But you can still
see and hear me!
Just who are you, anyway?
My name's Ashiya,
and I work part-time
for the Mononokean.
Wait, you actually
work for the Mononokean?
I need your help!
You gotta take me
there right now!
Please. Water.
[ASHIYA]
Is tea okay?
[JOMATSU]
Oh, yeah! Some more?
You must be really thirsty.
That's like your
fifth cup of tea.
I nearly died out there today.
But what an incredible
stroke of luck to be saved
by a real employee
of the Mononokean.
My name's Jomatsu, by the way.
Right before you lost
consciousness earlier,
you had mentioned something
about a princess.
I was referring to Princess
Anmo, the fairest of all.
Is that so?
Her beauty is beyond compare.
Long before I began to serve
her, many other yokai adored her
and dubbed her a princess.
But...
Her only flaw is she
falls in love too easily.
And always with those who
dwell in the mundane world.
She's been beguiled
by five humans,
fallen for fifteen birds,
seduced by four bears,
three tanuki,
two flying squirrels,
and too many cats
and dogs to count.
And pined away for a jet.
She's not very picky.
It does sound like she
falls in love very easily.
The worst part about
it is the aftermath.
Since creatures of the
mundane world can't see her,
the love is
tragically unrequited.
She's constantly
getting her heart broken.
And each time she feels
those pangs of torment,
she encloses herself
in an egg-shaped shell
and wallows in her solitude.
She hides inside an egg?
[JOMATSU]
Yes.
Normally she emerges after
a few days spent inside.
But it has been over
a month this time!
And what's more,
the shell continues to
grow larger by the day!
It's growing?
[JOMATSU] I just don't have
the strength to move it around
by myself anymore.
I'm completely useless to her!
[crying]
Please, Ashiya!
You must take me
to the Mononokean!
I'm sorry, but I'm actually
not able to just go there.
And why's that?
Well, Abeno.
The master of the Mononokean
has to summon it somewhere.
I can probably get
in touch with him.
But you should take
it easy for the night.
Very well.
But you must contact
him immediately!
This instant!
[ASHIYA] I wonder if
he'll pick up his phone.
[JOMATSU]
Keep calling him!
[ASHIYA]
I can't make him answer.
Hey.
You know you've got
something on your head?
Yeah, and I must've called
you like a million times
about it last night.
Why didn't you answer?
Are you the Master
of the Mononokean?
Yes. And who are you?
I'm Jomatsu.
He's been looking for you
so you can exorcise him.
If you can wait until I'm
finished with today's job,
I can help you out.
Or next week?
I can't wait that long!
We have a job today?
It's just a consultation
with a new client.
I don't think it'll go too late.
I'll be done by evening.
[ASHIYA]
He's working on our next job?
I see.
Evening, you say.
My poor princess.
[ASHIYA]
Oh, hey, Jomatsu.
What do you think of this?
We go over to where
Princess Anmo is,
and wait by her side
until he shows up.
Yeah! That's a great idea!
Let's go!
[ABENO]
Ashiya.
[ASHIYA]
Eh?
Are you sure?
You can handle that alone?
[ASHIYA]
He definitely isn't into it.
Let's get moving!
We're coming, Princess!
[ASHIYA]
Hold on, Jomatsu!
I can't fly! Come back!
Aww...
So... What should I do?
He's gone.
[ABENO]
It's not my problem.
Figure it out.
[ASHIYA panting]
[ASHIYA]
Jomatsu!
Wait up!
[JOMATSU]
You're way too slow!
I can't help you and
the princess if you keep
flying away!
[JOMATSU]
You can if you hurry!
[ASHIYA]
Give me a break!
If she hears that we
can go to the Underworld,
that might give the
princess enough initiative
to finally come
out of her shell.
It seems like an eternity
since I've seen her.
[ASHIYA] So he's been
waiting on her for a month,
but can't give me five minutes?
[ASHIYA coughs]
What? Something wrong?
No, it's fine!
Nothing to worry about!
[JOMATSU sighs]
Didn't sound like
things are fine.
What is it?
I really wasn't going
to ask, but uh...
Well, out with it!
Okay, the only thing is
that it's kind of a
personal question.
Are you in love
with the princess?
A very personal question!
And totally off base,
I might add!
I'm merely concerned
about her well-being.
I understand.
Must've gotten the wrong idea.
[JOMATSU]
Let's go!
[ASHIYA]
He's crazy for her.
[JOMATSU]
Princess! Princess! Princess!
That's strange.
I could've sworn that I left
her right under this tree.
What does the egg look like?
[JOMATSU] It's a little
bit bigger than me,
and completely
covered in stripes.
That means I gotta be careful.
I'd hate to step
on it and--[grunts]
No! Didn't hurt at all!
[JOMATSU]
Now what did you do to yourself?
My shin.
I hit it on a rock.
[JOMATSU]
A rock?
Are you positive?
[ASHIYA]
Could this be her egg?
[JOMATSU gasps]
Yes! This is it!
But the fact that it's grown so
much larger since the last time
I saw it completely
boggles my mind.
No kidding.
The thing's gigantic!
[JOMATSU]
Princess!
I've come to your aid!
I was able to locate
the Mononokean!
We can go to the Underworld!
Can she hear me?
In any case,
she's not coming out.
But I'm pretty sure the egg
will fit through the portal
to the Underworld, at least.
[ASHIYA grunts]
That is really heavy.
Man. It's gonna
be a real problem
trying to get it anywhere
with just us.
I'm afraid so.
Hold on.
Hey, Jomatsu?
Huh?
What do you say
we break it open?
Break it?
Well, the shell is
just crumbling away
like it's made out of sand.
So if we hit it with a rock,
we could get through it.
No, that would be
way too dangerous!
Oh, really?
Would it release some
poison gas or something?
I simply cannot risk
a shard breaking off
and hurting the princess!
Besides, she might come out
and peck us if we do that.
[ASHIYA] This guy's
speaking from experience.
Princess, I won't
let this guy hurt you!
I swore to protect
you with my life
if that's what I have to do.
Hey, can she hear us?
I mean, you've been
in this situation before.
So what happened then?
Let's see.
Well, in the past, sometimes
the princess would answer me
through the shell.
Then that should make
things really easy.
Um, hello?
I'm sorry to bother
you, Princess.
But I work for the Mononokean.
I know this is
a difficult time,
but I can't send you
to the Underworld
while you're inside your egg.
So if you could come out,
that would help us out a lot.
[knocking]
Hey, can you hear me
in there, Princess?
[JOMATSU] You're gonna break
it if you're not careful!
I think she's ignoring me.
[JOMATSU]
I suppose it can't be helped.
I'll just have to give up
going to the Underworld
and wait for her to
come out when she's ready.
Are you sure?
[JOMATSU]
Yes.
[ASHIYA] I know it's
not what you want.
But...
Ashiya, wait a sec.
[ASHIYA]
It's the only option we have.
No, don't!
This just means that you
won't have to wait for her.
[JOMATSU]
What?!
That is completely out of the
question! I won't allow it!
You can't keep letting her
get away with this behavior!
Sometimes you just have
to be cruel to be kind!
[JOMATSU]
What's gotten into you?
Put that down!
[ASHIYA]
Get out of the way, Jomatsu!
I don't want you getting hurt!
[JOMATSU]
Don't be ridiculous!
I said it's too dangerous!
[ASHIYA] Unless we do something
now, this is never gonna end!
[JOMATSU]
I can wait as long as I have to!
[ASHIYA]
Well, I have a job to do,
and it's not just
you I have to please!
I can't make Abeno angry again!
[JOMATSU]
If you hurt the princess,
you're gonna make me angry,
and I'll hurt you!
[ASHIYA]
Get out of the way, Jomatsu!
[JOMATSU, ASHIYA grunting]
[JOMATSU yells]
[ASHIYA]
Oh, my gosh!
I'm so sorry!
I-I didn't mean to hit you!
[ASHIYA]
Jomatsu. Can you hear me?
[PRINCESS ANMO chirps]
[PRINCESS ANMO chirping]
[JOMATSU gasps]
Princess!
Hello, there.
Nice to meet you, Princess.
Jomatsu's fine. So don't worry.
[PRINCESS ANMO chirps]
Did she really just go back in?
[JOMATSU]
Are you kidding me?!
You mean you went
through that whole routine
with your horrible acting
because you thought
you could trick her?
[ASHIYA]
I knew it was risky.
But I didn't want you to
have to wait any longer.
Princess Amno?
I know you can hear me.
Please listen.
You came out because
you were worried
about Jomatsu, right?
Honestly, I'm
worried about him too.
He works so hard.
I didn't want him to collapse
on the sidewalk again.
Slow down!
Don't tell lies about me!
I don't want the princess
getting the wrong idea.
[PRINCESS ANMO chirping]
Well, uh...
The princess. What did she say?
She asked me,
"Did you truly push yourself
to the brink over me? Why?"
[ASHIYA]
Because you love her, obviously.
This is it.
Your chance to tell her
how you feel about her.
[JOMATSU gasps]
My chance? That's absurd!
And how would that be?
Don't play dumb.
You're gonna blow it if
you act like you don't care.
The whole reason she asked you
is because she thinks she
already knows the answer.
So tell her.
[JOMATSU]
You think so?
[PRINCESS ANMO chirps]
Princess, I...
It's all because...
Well... I did it because...
Honestly...
Because... I love it.
I love flying through
the sky with you
more than anything.
It's what makes every
single day worth living!
[JOMATSU] The joy that I
feel when we're in the air...
It's worth it!
That's what makes
the wait bearable!
So even after we
go to the Underworld,
all I want more than anything
that I've ever wanted
is just the chance
to be by your side.
My dear princess.
Forever might not
be long enough for me!
Oh...!
[ASHIYA] Well, he certainly
didn't hold back on that one!
The cat is out of the bag now.
[PRINCESS ANMO chirping]
[JOMATSU]
Come on, Princess.
You don't have to humor me.
Really!
[PRINCESS ANMO chirping]
Oh. Is that true?
I had no idea you
felt the same way!
[ASHIYA]
Steam?
Hey... Ashiya,
if you can... Water.
Please, more water.
All I have is Oolong tea.
[ABENO]
Ashiya.
[ASHIYA]
Whoa! You're here already?
If you want me to leave,
that can easily be arranged.
No! This is perfect timing!
[ABENO]
There's another one?
I'd like you to
meet Princess Anmo.
So she was inside the egg?
We were finally able to
convince her to come out.
All that's left is to send
them to the Underworld.
[ABENO] That's the smug look of
a guy who finally figured out
how to solve a
problem by himself.
You fool.
[ASHIYA]
Huh?
[PRINCESS ANMO chirps]
Princess?
[PRINCESS ANMO chirping]
[ASHIYA] She looks way
too happy up there.
What's going on here?
Didn't you and the princess just
confess your undying love
for one another?
Well...
Specifically, what she told
me was that she loved
flying with me more
than anything else, too.
Yeah?
[JOMATSU] She also said
she'd try not to hide
in her shell anymore.
That wasn't actually
the issue here!
Do neither of you get it?
This was about more
than flying together!
Come on!
So... what's wrong?
Don't act like you
don't know what's going on!
You're caught up in this
bizarre love triangle now, too!
I've only been here a
couple of minutes, ya know.
I was trying to get
them an Underworld
honeymoon and storybook ending!
And then you showed up
at the absolute worst time!
[ABENO]
What?!
[ABENO] Everything about
today totally sucks.
This stupid job.
And the next one
is gonna be even worse.
[ASHIYA]
He's so loud and childish.
And I thought he was honest,
but it's more like precocious.
[ABENO]
What is it now?
Reflecting on your own flaws?
[ASHIYA]
It's not me!
I'm talking about Yahiko!
[ABENO] Well, I couldn't
tell the difference.
[ASHIYA]
What do you mean by that?