[OKINA] So then,
you've made up your mind?
[TOMORI]
Yes.
[OKINA]
Very well.
I shall go to the
Mononokean at once.
[TOMORI]
Thank you so much.
I only wish I could go myself.
[OKINA] It's been given me to
understand the Mononokean
has a new employee.
I look forward to having a face
to go along with the rumor.
[TOMORI]
Do be careful on your way.
An unmistakable smell.
Rain is coming. Count on it.
[OKINA] I certainly know better
than to doubt your nose.
Ah! Fuzzy!
I'm so glad you're
back to normal!
[ZENKO] Does he always
cry when he's happy?
[ABENO]
Ugh. Get a hold of yourself!
Have some self-respect!
I can't help it
if I get emotional!
Just let me express myself!
If Fuzzy's back to normal,
then must be the
same for Yahiko.
[footsteps]
[ZENKO]
Hey, Dad.
[ASHIYA]
This isn't good.
[ZENKO'S DAD]
Yeah, so, uh...
You kids have any
idea how late it is?
What're you doing
in place like this?
If it's abandoned, there's a
probably a damn good reason!
He is pissed.
What do we say?
I dunno!
--[loud crack]
--[ZENKO'S DAD groans]
Hold on to Fuzzy for a second.
What's wrong?
[ZENKO'S DAD]
I threw out my back!
--[loud crack]
--[groans]
It was fine when
I left the temple.
What is it?
[ABENO]
Fun's over Yahiko.
No fair!
You saw where I was!
How the--?
Are you doing
this to my dad?
[YAHIKO]
Hey, Haruitsuki!
I can shape-shift!
I'm back to my old self!
We can play hide-and-seek again!
[ASHIYA]
Oh, that's right.
You were super gigantic
earlier. I forgot.
What?!
You're such a jerk, Ashiya!
Yeah, yeah. My bad.
Hey, let's get you off of there.
No!
Excuse me?
I don't think so!
If you want me to force
you, have it your way!
I want Haruitsuki to carry me!
Let go!
[ASHIYA]
You're being a brat!
Who the hell you talkin' to?
[ASHIYA]
Crap!
Help me out here?
No way.
[ZENKO'S DAD]
My back pain's gone.
What the--?
Well, you see, sir,
I'm kind of an introvert,
so I talk to myself a lot.
That's it. Sure. I was just
thinking out loud...
[ZENKO'S DAD]
Wait a minute.
When I couldn't stop laughing,
this kid showed up out
of the blue and fixed it.
It's something
I do all the time.
[ZENKO'S DAD]
Straight answer.
Did you just heal my back?
What?
How are you with
high blood pressure?
Can you cure that, too?
You might wanna see
a doctor about that one.
A-ha! So you did fix
my back! I knew it!
We should probably step in
and help him at some point.
[ASHIYA]
What do I do?
If I tell him it was a yokai ,
he'll think I'm
screwing with him!
Dad, leave him alone.
[ZENKO'S DAD]
Huh?
[ZENKO]
Hanae can see spirits.
There was a ghost on your back.
He saw it and figured he'd
take care of it for you.
A ghost?!
No kidding?
You saw it on my back?
Wha...
What was it doing there
in the first place?
Oh. I, uh...
I don't know, but it was there.
[ZENKO'S DAD gasps]
Dad can't see spirits,
but he's a total believer.
Mom used to say the idea
scared him half to death.
Poor guy can't even sit
through a horror movie.
Makes you wonder
why he became a monk.
[ZENKO'S DAD]
That's it!
Come and work for me
at the temple!
[ASHIYA]
What?
Folks come in off the street
requesting exorcisms
all the time!
I need you!
Actually, sir, uh...
Hey! Abeno!
You can hear him, can't you?
[ABENO]
Yep.
C'mon, Ashida. Please?
[ASHIYA]
It's Ashiya.
Zenko.
Did something good happen?
What's going on?
Seems kind of weird,
don't you think?
Mm-hmm.
It's a little weird.
But it is pretty good.
Dad doesn't wanna kill Hanae.
In fact, he's practically
gushing over him.
Anyway...
What the hell were
you doing with Zenko?
Not what it looks like!
Is he...?
Mm-hmm.
Uh-oh.
[ABENO]
We should get going.
And Yahiko?
I'm not playing with you.
[YAHIKO]
Aww!
Doesn't look like it's
gonna let up any time soon.
[ABENO] Least we got back
before it started pouring.
Lucky us.
That old man didn't
wanna let you leave.
[ASHIYA]
Don't put that on me!
I didn't know it
was supposed to rain.
Incidentally, I didn't
bring an umbrella.
Can the Mononokean
give me a lift?
[bell ringing]
[ASHIYA]
Little steep, don't you think?
[ASHIYA chuckles]
[ABENO]
A guest?
No one made an
appointment today.
[ASHIYA]
Be right there!
Welcome!
[OKINA]
Hello.
[OKINA] Raining rather
a lot this evening
in the mundane world, isn't it?
[ABENO]
It's Okina.
[ASHIYA]
Boss. Do we have any towels?
Maybe some hot tea?
[OKINA gulping]
[OKINA]
Sorry to drop in like this.
It's fine.
[OKINA] And apologies
for being so drenched.
I fell into a puddle
on the way here.
[laughs] The skies won't clear
for a few hours, I'm told.
You don't say.
[OKINA]
Excuse me, young sir,
but are you the new employee?
Oh, yes.
My name's Ashiya.
[OKINA]
Nice to meet you.
My name is Inogaratake
Yuuhi Takino Okinakami.
Wait... "Kami"?
Are you a god?
[OKINA laughs]
Gracious, no.
Just an old yokai .
Humans tend to
inflate my status.
Call me Okina, please.
[bell ringing]
So, have you always lived
in the mundane world?
[OKINA laughs]
Well, I'm fond enough of it
that I selfishly
requested to stay.
Which brings me to the purpose
of my unannounced visit
this evening, Abeno.
A yokai in need of your help is
waiting for us near the shrine.
I assume there's a reason
you didn't bring them?
Why'd you leave them behind?
[OKINA] I'm afraid the poor
dear doesn't have the use
of her eyes.
Whoa.
I don't understand.
What exactly are you getting at?
[OKINA] Sight comes to
her only through vision
of human beings
able to see yokai .
On loan, so to speak.
She needs to borrow the
sight of someone like you.
[OKINA laughs] It sounds
a lot graver than it is.
She's not asking much.
Just to be exorcised
and sent to the Underworld.
Forgive my indiscretion.
[OKINA] Besides,
it's not a painful process.
The person who grants
their vision to her
has it back in a matter of days.
[ABENO]
Very well.
I humbly accept your request.
[OKINA]
We'd be grateful if you wait
until after the skies clear.
For the time being,
might I impose on you
for another cup of tea?
[ABENO]
It would be my pleasure.
Stay as long as you wish.
[OKINA laughs]
How kind.
I believe I'll make
myself at home, then.
Thank you.
[TOMORI]
What's that I hear?
Footsteps. Okina.
He brings two others.
[OKINA]
Thank you for waiting.
You must be Master Abeno
of the Mononokean.
Indeed I am,
and you must be Tomori,
am I right?
Yes.
I appreciate your assistance
more than you could know.
Happy to be of help.
Am I mistaken, or did I hear
another set of footsteps?
[OKINA] That would be
his employee, Ashiya.
[TOMORI] Yes, of course.
Good to meet you.
It's good to meet
you, too, ma'am.
[TOMORI] I'm grateful the
two of you could come.
Excuse me if I
cut right to the chase,
but I'm afraid this area's
not quite big enough
for me to open a portal.
Would it be possible for
us to take this business
somewhere else, perhaps?
If need be.
Here, I'll help lead you.
[TOMORI gasps]
A human?
You're gifted with the
ability to see yokai .
It's been ages.
I can't remember the
last time I encountered
one of you here in
the mundane world.
Uh... Um...
Do you mind if I ask how long
you've been without sight?
[TOMORI]
I don't know.
Quite some time, surely.
I'm embarrassed to admit it's
been so long I can't remember.
Yet...
I remember all the things I've
seen in the mundane world.
Its beauty is unsurpassed.
I could exist for
millennia and not forget.
If only I could stay here.
Alas, it's become too difficult.
Shame, but I must go back.
I hope returning
to the Underworld
will restore my sight.
I miss being able
to take everything in.
[ASHIYA]
Why is he glaring at me?
Uh, Tomori?
Sorry to keep
getting all personal.
But don't hold back on me, 'kay?
Would you like to see
the mundane world again?
Before you leave?
You misunderstood!
That isn't what I was trying
to imply in the least!
I'm sorry.
Please don't worry about me.
[ASHIYA]
No, it's fine!
You don't have to be sorry!
I just knew if didn't
put it out there,
I'd kick myself for not asking!
Kick yourself?
I thought maybe you
really wanted to see
this world again before you
go and just couldn't ask.
I had to be sure, y'know?
I'd have regretted not offering.
Besides, and I don't mean
this to sound patronizing
or anything.
But I thought if all it cost
me was not seeing yokai
for a few days...
Well...
It's not too big a deal. Right?
[ASHIYA]
He didn't shoot it down.
That's a good sign.
[TOMORI sighs]
To be completely honest,
I would love to look upon this
world one last time before I go.
If you would be so kind,
May I borrow your sight?
[TOMORI] Ashiya.
Close your eyes for me.
Sure.
Hey, where'd they go?
Oh. That's right.
That was the condition,
wasn't it?
What about her?
Can Tomori see the world?
Yes. You should go home.
[ASHIYA]
What? But...
If you can't see yokai ,
you'll only get in my way.
[ASHIYA] You don't have
to say it like that!
I'm doing my job!
What would you have
done without your--?
[ABENO]
Watch where you step.
I'm sorry, Fuzzy!
When you can see yokai again,
I'll put you back to work.
Till then, go home.
[ASHIYA]
Fine. I'll get out of your hair.
[OKINA]
Tomori, can you see?
Yes!
The sky, the clouds,
the flowers.
All of it's so breathtaking!
I'm overwhelmed!
Please, Abeno.
Give Ashiya my heartfelt thanks.
I'm so very grateful.
Tell him I departed for the
Underworld free of regrets.
Won't you?
Yes.
[ASHIYA]
I'm home.
How was your day?
Sweetie? What's wrong?
Nothing.
[ASHIYA'S MOM]
Hmm... Okay.
He looks like he
lost his best friend.
[ASHIYA] It's rough not
being able to see Fuzzy
and the Mononokean.
Oh, well.
It's only for a few days.
I'll power through.
[ASHIYA'S MOM]
Purple coneflowers.
Aren't they gorgeous?
They say
"I will heal your pain."
What're you
talking about, Mom?
I'm not in any kind of pain.
You do seem a bit better.
Best be goin'. See you later.
Have fun at school!
[ASHIYA'S MOM]
That's a relief.
It's finally been three days.
Man, talk about
feeling like forever!
Woo-hoo!
Can't wait to cuddle with Fuzzy!
[ASHIYA]
Seriously?
I don't think you've ever
gotten here earlier than me.
I'm surprised you're awake.
So. It's been three days,
which means my second sight
should be back to normal!
Yeah, well it's not.
[ASHIYA]
Uh...
What is that supposed to mean?
Is Fuzzy here?
Yes. He just jumped on you.
Where is he?
I can't see him!
Why can't I see him?
Guess it's gonna take
longer than we thought.
Fuzzy. I'm sorry.
[ASHIYA]
Two days later.
Your left!
Nice try, but he's sitting
smack dab on top
of your head.
[ASHIYA]
Ah!
He was supposed
to be in your hand!
No fair! You tricked me!
You wouldn't have fallen for it
if you could actually see him.
We're done for the day,
so go home.
[ASHIYA]
I don't understand.
It's been five whole days now.
Why can't I see him yet?
Okina and Tomori didn't seem
the type to pull one over on me.
So you can't see 'em
and you can't hear 'em.
That's great.
Hear them?
Nothing. Don't worry about it.
[ASHIYA]
What am I gonna do?
This sucks!
How much longer do I have to
wait till I can see Fuzzy again?
Damn! There has to be some
way to restore my sight!
Ashiya.
Yeah?
That's enough.
Wait... What do you mean?
[ABENO]
It's time for you to quit.
Look, I'm willing to keep
you on until I can find
your replacement.
It's just...
I don't have anything you
can help with right now.
Guys in my position can't
afford to get sentimental
or complacent.
Truth is, I'm bad
enough tolerating people
who are useful to me,
let alone dead weight.
Am I really useless?
It's been five days. That's all.
And already he's...
[ASHIYA] So you're letting
me go, is that it?
[ASHIYA]
I get it, okay?
I can't see yokai .
I don't blame you for
wanting to find someone else.
There's not much I
can do for you like this.
Still, though.
"Dead weight?"
Where the hell do you get off?
I didn't come to you
looking for a job.
I came to you for help.
Next thing I know, boom.
Suddenly I have to work off
a massive debt, or else.
Being able to see yokai
terrified me at first,
but I've changed.
When by ability returns,
we'll pick up where we left off!
That's a promise.
Before this is all over, you'll
be on your hands and knees
begging me to come back!
You're gonna have
to work really hard
to make that happen.
Wouldn't hold my
breath if I were you.
[ZENKO]
What happened to your face?
Stupid Ashiya
hit me with his shoe!
I hate him! He's a meanie!
[ZENKO]
That doesn't sound like him.
So, what did you
end up buying?
Lemon drops and a croquette.
And some coffee.
Aw, man. I should've
gotten a croquette.
[FUSSHI] What's up?
You're not gonna get anything?
No appetite.
[FUSSHI]
You seem a little tired.
Do you need a pick-me-up?
How about some coffee?
Here, take mine.
That's so nice of you.
Thanks a lot.
[SAGA]
You should take a look at this.
[ASHIYA]
Oh, yeah?
Wanted ads?
Figured you could use it
to find yourself a job.
But I haven't been
fired from my old one.
Not yet.
Let's face it, man,
it's only a matter of time.
Well that all depends on me.
Why get a job when
you could join a club?
What kind of club?
Photography's been really cool.
[ASHIYA]
Before I started high school,
that's exactly the sort
of thing I saw myself doing.
Then Abeno started eating
up all of my free time.
[SAGA]
I'm thinking nature stuff.
[ASHIYA] Now, though...
What's stopping me?
[SAGA]
Really? Let's do it!
[TEACHER 11A] Solving for a
system of linear inequalities
requires finding values for
each of the variables...
[ASHIYA]
Did Abeno take the day off?
Maybe he's on a job.
Good for him.
Not that I care
one way or the other.
Please. Who am I kidding?
This is torture.
Feels like I've been
left out in the cold.
I'm not ready to let go yet.
[bell ringing]
Why wouldn't I be?
Right. I'm off.
Hey.
Hey, there!
Koura, come look!
He's here! It's Itsuki!
Ah, darling!
You're back sooner
than expected.
[KOURA]
Don't worry.
We took care to
whip up some extra
so there won't be
a repeat of last time.
Appreciate it.
That's right,
I haven't told you.
The screeching yokai 's
doing better.
That's good to hear.
I think he really
misses you and Ashiya.
Ah.
Speaking of Ashiya,
why isn't he with you today?
Oh, yeah. Y'know, I was just
thinking it seemed a little
on the quiet side.
Afraid I had to
leave him behind.
That's too bad.
Is he feeling okay?
I wanted to say hi.
Yes, quite a shame.
Such a lovely pair
of ears that boy has.
Well, not as lovely as mine,
but they're all right.
Hey, Shizuku.
What's up?
[ABENO]
Is your brother around?
Not here.
He's over at Newt Lake.
Business with the Legislator?
Nah.
I just thought I'd
drop by and say hello.
Kind of curious to see
what he's up to these days.
Good seeing you, ladies.
[SHIZUKU]
Aw! You're leaving already?
Sorry. Wish I could stay.
We'll visit longer
next time, I promise.
Of course.
Pleasure as always.
Darken our door
whenever you wish.
And bring dear
Ashiya along, won't you?
Hard to believe he's going
to see the Legislator
of his own free will.
Huh. Very odd.
Very odd indeed.
It's been a while. Or has it?
[ASHIYA]
Hey, Zenko?
Question: How d'you get Yahiko
to help around the temple?
[ZENKO] I brush his hair,
give him treats,
take him for walks
when he gets bored.
Stuff like that.
When he feels like it,
he pitches in.
[ASHIYA] So he's less of a
helper and more of a pet.