[ABENO sighs]
[ASHIYA] That sigh means
I'm about to get a lecture.
I know he said keep
a low profile, but still.
Telling her was
the right thing to do.
He has to agree
with me on that.
[ASHIYA]
Here it comes.
"You can't follow orders!
You're like a child!"
That's what he'll say.
[gulps]
[ASHIYA]
Oh, man.
He's about to explode with rage.
Back away slowly.
[ABENO]
Nice work. Thank you.
[ASHIYA]
Uh...?
[coughing]
What's wrong?
[ASHIYA]
Seriously?!
Yes. What the hell's
gotten into you?
What did that mean?
You actually said "thank you."
Yes. What do you mean,
"What did it mean?"
You found the ring. Nice going.
Calm down.
You earned your keep today.
If I'd been working on my own,
there wouldn't have been
a happily ever after.
Seemed appropriate
to say "thank you."
I don't know about you, but
I'm marking this one down
as "achievement unlocked."
[ASHIYA]
"Achievement?"
I kinda feel like maybe
you're praising me.
Uh-oh. You must
not be feeling well.
Are you dying?
[ABENO]
No. And unless you want to be,
take the damn compliment.
[ASHIYA] Ah. There's
the Abeno I'm used to.
[ABENO]
You're a jackass.
[ASHIYA laughing]
What? Knock if off already.
You're creeping me out.
[ASHIYA]
Sorry.
It's just, you've never actually
given me a compliment before.
I'm not sure I know
how to handle it.
[laughing]
[ASHIYA]
I've got the giggles!
[laughing]
Totally involuntary, I swear!
[ASHIYA laughing]
Huh? What is it?
--[slapping noise]
--[ASHIYA] Ow!
[ABENO]
There, problem solved.
[ASHIYA]
You slapped me in the face!
[ABENO] You're not
giggling anymore, are you?
[ASHIYA]
Well, no, but...!
So tired.
[ASHIYA] Exorcist stuff for
days on end without a break.
Homework.
Help around the shop.
I can't keep this up
for much longer.
[ZENKO]
Hanae.
[ASHIYA] If I don't watch it,
they'll start calling me
"that kid from the
nurse's office" again.
[ZENKO]
Hanae.
[ASHIYA]
Uh-huh?
Must be hearing things.
Good morning.
Zenko, what--?
Volume.
My bad. Sorry.
Oh, that's right.
I forgot you and I
go to the same school.
How'd you know I was in
this particular class, though?
I just asked
around some, is all.
You have a reputation.
Guy next to me called you "that
kid from the nurse's office."
Goodie. It's made it
to the other classes.
Listen.
Thanks for helping
the other day.
I meant to say it then,
but I didn't get the chance.
It's okay. No thanks needed.
I helped 'cause I wanted to.
Wait, so that's it?
I mean, is that the whole reason
you bothered to track me down?
Uh... Well, yeah.
For starters, I guess. Hey.
Hey.
Aren't you that little girl?
The one who lives
in the Seiryuji temple?
You were the kimono guy
hiding in our closet, right?
Name's Abeno. Pleasure.
Oh, I'm Zenko Fujiwara.
Nice to meet you.
--She's a high school student?
--He's a high school student?
I'm glad that I ran
into both of you today.
There's something
I wanted to ask about.
Do you know what this is?
A tattoo?
[ZENKO]
No.
Looks like a bite mark.
Does it hurt?
[ZENKO]
Not really.
But you can see it? It's there?
I showed a few other people,
but they couldn't see a thing.
Doctor had a look at it, too.
Told me I was fine,
and that it was all in my head.
But if Abeno and I can see
it, then clearly that means...
[ABENO] Zenko, look out
the window for a second.
Notice anything strange?
[ASHIYA]
Sure do.
[ZENKO]
Hanae.
Is that one of the yokai
you were telling me about
the other day?
You can see it too?
[ZENKO]
Not just that one.
Since the dog bit me,
I've seen them everywhere.
The dog?
[ZENKO]
That might not be the best word.
I'm not totally sure.
The bite came out of nowhere.
Could've very well been
a yokai in dog form.
Did you happen to get a look?
Afterwards.
There was, like,
smoke all around.
The ears were huge.
Now that I think about it,
it was more of a...
Fox, maybe?
[FOX]
Oopsie!
Rude! Didn't see that coming.
What's the big idea?
That's what I was gonna ask you.
Who in the hell are you?
[ABENO]
Impossible...
I didn't sense him
until he touched me.
[ASHIYA] Why is Abeno
all freaked out?
That can't be a good omen.
[ABENO] I've never met a
yokai in the mundane world
so in control of its own power.
How long since one was reported?
A hundred years?
I guess monsters do still exist.
[FOX]
Hello, there.
In case you were wondering...
I bit the girl.
Haruitsuki!
Don't be that way!
You haven't forgotten about me.
I'm guessing there some kind
of history between you two?
Is he one of your clients?
You do business with
a lot of these things.
If he were a client,
I'd remember.
[FOX] Meh. Kind of
makes sense you don't.
You were just a widdle-biddy
thing back then.
And I look a lot
different than I used to.
Sounds like I was right.
Well, it's fine.
You not remembering
won't hurt anything.
Heh. After all, I've only
come here to play with you.
Things are just so terribly
boring these days.
You don't mind playing
with me for a while,
do you, old friend?
Is he serious?
Then again...
It's not like you can turn
down my invitation, now, is it?
[ZENKO gasps]
[ASHIYA]
Zenko!
[FOX] Between letting your
friend's arm waste away
and indulging a simple request,
it seems pretty obvious to me
which option you'll go with.
Now... What do ya say?
Lets play some hide-and-seek
like in the old days, huh?
It's gonna be loads of fun!
Do it and I'll remove the mark.
That's all you want?
[FOX]
Yep! Easy peasy.
You know the rules?
Really?
Don't tell me this is the
first time you've heard of it!
Ugh. If you're a noob,
you can move along.
I only want people who
know hide-and-seek.
I know how to play
hide-and-seek!
Give me some credit!
I killed it in middle school!
[ZENKO]
Middle school?
[ABENO]
In other words, last year.
Oh, good.
So you do know
how the game works.
Excellent. Great.
I'll hide.
You three are "it." Ready?
Hang on.
The three of us can't just drop
everything to play with you.
Why not? How come?
[whining]
No fair! I wanna play!
C'mon! No, no, no, no, no!
Either we do hide--
Zenko, please.
If we don't do
what the fox wants,
you may be stuck
with that mark forever.
Oh, well.
[FOX] Come on! I'm bored!
Just play with me!
[ASHIYA] Wow. He's throwing
a straight-up tantrum.
We can't play now.
[FOX]
How come?
We're in school.
We have classes to get to.
So what?
Who cares about school?
Let's play!
[ZENKO]
Sorry.
If you wanna play with us,
it'll have to wait till later.
For now just go to my family's
temple and be patient.
When school gets out,
hide-and-seek it is.
[FOX sighs]
'Kay, fine.
He's cool with that?
[ZENKO]
Good boy.
Yeah, yeah.
Just be there after
school gets out.
[ABENO]
Wait.
I don't think
I caught your name.
Sorry if I don't recognize you.
If you told me
your name, though...
[FOX] Better if you try to
remember on you own, Haruitsuki.
[ASHIYA]
He's gone.
I wish I knew what he
was getting out of all this.
Doesn't seem to me
like the Underworld
is on his list of priorities.
Yeah, it's weird.
Maybe he just really loves
playing hide-and-seek.
One thing's for sure...
Our priority is getting that
mark removed pronto.
You're right.
So we'll go to my place
after school's out. And play.
[phone ringing]
[ASHIYA]
Dark. Deserted.
Creepy statues.
Charming place at night.
Answer your phone, Abeno!
Ugh. Of all the days
for this to happen.
Okay.
So, any volunteers to
help me organize files
after class today?
[STUDENTS groan]
[HOMEROOM TEACHER 1A]
Great. Perfect.
Ashiya it is.
Me?
Since you were out
the first week of class,
this will be an opportunity
to catch up on everything
you missed back then.
[ASHIYA] That'd be great,
sir, except that, um,
well, I kind of
already have plans.
Uh, right, Abeno?
Huh? You don't need
to be there, actually.
I'll just take the hairball
with me. It's fine.
[ASHIYA]
Huh?
[ASHIYA] Like I'm gonna
let you do this on your own.
If you haven't figured it
out yet, I'm a worrier.
It's so late, are they still
playing hide-and-seek,
or is everything cool?
Might help if you picked up!
Should'a thought to ask
Zenko for her number.
Hey, Abeno!
Zenko!
You guys still playing
hide-and-seek, or what?
I'm here!
[ASHIYA] Am I crazy, or did
something hit me in the back
just now?
Where is everybody?
Nothing lying around
that could'a done it.
If it was a yokai ,
I'd have seen them.
Is this place haunted?
My back!
Something definitely
poked my back!
Oh my god, it's a ghost!
Wait, what the--?
Fuzzy?
Oh, thank goodness.
You scared the heck out of me.
I thought you were a ghost.
[ZENKO] How are you fine
with yokai but not ghosts?
[ASHIYA]
There you are!
C'mon over here.
[bell rings]
[ASHIYA]
Um... Okay.
We're playing hide-and-seek
in a graveyard.
Lot of places to hide.
Isn't it bad luck?
Wow. It's so dark
I can't see where it ends.
Abeno was walking around
this section a little while ago,
I think.
[ASHIYA]
There he is.
[ABENO]
Found you.
Hey.
[FOX]
Aw! You're too good at this.
Did that headstone just talk?
Abeno!
Nice job, Haruitsuki.
You found me!
Next time I'll find an
even better place to hide.
[ASHIYA]
Wait, did...?
Did the fox change
himself into a headstone?
Oh, hi. Did you just get here?
You're late.
Yeah, I know.
Looks like I missed
a pretty fun game.
Oh, well.
Whaddya say you go on and remove
the mark from Zenko's arm?
[FOX]
Again!
Just one more round!
What's he doing?
Where did he go?
We were supposed to have a deal!
I thought you played with him!
I suck at this.
Fuzzy found him twice.
Abeno twenty times now.
Yeah?
Whenever we find him, he
always insists on going again.
Why else do you think
Abeno looks like somebody's
run him over?
[ABENO sighs]
"One more round," huh?
You know, I thought
he looked a little tired.
Well, you can take
a break now, Abeno!
The hide-and-seek
champion has arrived!
Oh. By the way,
I was gonna ask.
The fox ringing
any bells yet, or...?
[ABENO]
No, not really.
I've figured out
a few things, though.
He's able to transform himself
into a variety of shapes,
like the headstone.
He's good a concealing
his presence, too.
Bizarre.
[ABENO] Oh, and like
someone else we know,
he behaves like a five-year-old.
[ASHIYA] Could you please stop
glaring at me like that?
[ABENO]
Whatever.
Just keep playing until
the fox is satisfied.
Oh-ho! Don't you worry, boss!
When I'm done, he'll be
sick of hide-and-seek!
You're really raring
to go, aren't you?
[ASHIYA]
So what's the trick?
How have you been able
to lock onto him
when he's not in his fox form?
I just wander around.
When I'm getting warmer, I can
feel it in the back of my mind.
All right!
Easy enough.
Just wander around.
[ASHIYA]
Um, anybody care to join me?
You're choking me.
Ugh. Getting anything?
[ASHIYA]
Not yet, but I'm looking.
[FOX]
Again!
[ZENKO]
Oh, come on.
We were just over there.
[ASHIYA] I didn't feel
anything different.
Hey, Abeno!
We're not picking up on him,
even when we're close!
[ABENO]
What?
I can't hear you!
[ASHIYA] I said we're
not picking up on him
even when we're close!
[ABENO]
'Cause you're not focusing!
So we have to focus now?
I guess, but what are
we supposed to focus on?
It's like Zen meditation.
If we just clear our
minds, concentrate,
and sharpen our senses, then...
...we should be all set.
Yeah. Good plan.
Whoa! I felt something!
Like I was being drawn in.
What do you see?
Nothing, but I think I might
know where he's hiding.
This path will take
us straight to him.
I assume I'm leading?
We have to hurry!
[ZENKO]
Don't push.
It's okay.
Let me just try it again.
Heads up.
[ASHIYA]
What are you doing?
[ABENO]
Shh!
All right, here's the thing.
He's disguised himself
as a grave marker again.
If we want this to end,
we're gonna have to catch him.
Yeah, I guess so.
But isn't he gonna
throw a tantrum?
[ABENO] We're not making
any headway like this.
Maybe yoko 'll listen to reason.
Well, hey.
At least knowing his name
gives us something to go on!
[ABENO]
Huh?
You called him "Yoko" just now.
Oh, uh... That's
not his actual name.
Yoko is really just another
way of saying a "fox yokai ."
Ah. That's news to me.
That's something
you should know.
How has a servant
of the Mononokean
never heard of a yoko ?
Mononokean?
[ASHIYA]
"Servant?"
[ABENO sighs]
Anyway...
If we're gonna catch him,
we have to be sneaky
about it, all right?
Last thing we want is for
him to see what we're up to.
So, to be on the safe side,
you, Zenko, and Fuzzy
hide somewhere nearby.
Sounds good.
Have you got a better idea?
Not really.
This just seems...
I dunno.
Sorry if I'm wrong.
'Bout what?
[ASHIYA]
Well...
Found you. Game over.
Um... What're you talking about?
Ha! I knew it!
No way he'd be so calm!
I don't know if
I'm the best judge.
I've only met the guy twice.
You're a moron.
[ASHIYA]
Wait...
Now he's acting normal.
Okay.
Fine. You got me.
Abeno?
Dang it.
I was so sure you
wouldn't figure it out, too.
I thought shape-shifting
into Haruitsuki
for a round or two would be a
good way to keep things fresh.
So much for that.
Well, let's go again!
[ASHIYA]
Time out!
We can't keep doing this!
Abeno!
I caught the yoko !
[ABENO] I can't make out
what you're saying.
[ASHIYA] Can you just
come over here, please?
Argh! What's your problem?
Look, I'll keep playing
hide-and-seek with you,
but first you've got to erase
the mark you put on Zenko!
[ZENKO]
Wow.
How'd you figure out
it wasn't Abeno?
I would've never known.
I dunno.
Guess something just
seemed a little off to me.
My transformation
was a dead-ringer!
It wasn't about how you looked.
You called me a servant.
Abeno always says "employee."
While we're at it, he also
doesn't call Fuzzy "Fuzzy."
Ever.
[ZENKO]
What does he call him?
[ASHIYA]
Hairball.
[ABENO]
Guys.
What the hell's
going on over here--?
What?
What am I holding in my arms?
The hairball.
All right, then.
He's the real thing.
See?
[FOX] You won't be
able to tell next time!
Huh?
Aw! Haruitsuki!
Ashiya said he wouldn't
play with me anymore!
That's not true!
You're lying!
That's not what I said!
I told you I'd keep playing
after you remove Zenko's mark!
You say that, but once
I do, you'll just run off!
You'll have to play with me
for three whole days first!
Three days? In a row?
We're gonna be stuck
playing hide-and-seek with him
for the rest of our lives.
[ABENO]
Three days...
Wait a minute...
That's it!
[VOICE]
Hey. I know you.
You're the kid from
the Mononokean.
Do you wanna play?
[FOX yelling]
[ASHIYA]
That's not how it works!
No! We're playing!
We're playing! We're playing!
I don't have a choice.
We have to go to school!
School's dumb!
Play, or her mark
stays there forever!
[ABENO]
Yahiko?
Of course!
You're Yahiko!
Haruitsuki.
I thought you forgot.
You do remember my name!
--[ASHIYA] What the...?
--[ZENKO] Hanae!
[ASHIYA]
No! He's trying to hide again!
[YAHIKO]
Not this time.
Ooh!
Walking on all fours
really wears you out.
Sure took you long enough
to remember who I am.
What did you expect?
This is my first time ever
seeing you in fox form.
I guess we both look
pretty different now, huh?
You've gotten so tall.
How long has it been?
About thirty years?
Thirty years?
I hadn't even been
born thirty years ago.
It's only been eight years.
Right around the time that
I first became an employee
of the Mononokean.
[ASHIYA] Abeno starting doing
exorcisms eight years ago?
How old would he
have been back then?
Seven?
[ASHIYA] You've been working
since you were seven?
What kind of debt
are you paying off?
I didn't start the way you did.
Who was the master of the
Mononokean back in those days?
If I remember correctly,
it was Aoi, isn't that so?
Aoi?
Look at'cha now.
Who'd've ever thought
you'd be the master?
Lots of rumors floating around
about how that happened.
Eight years, huh?
How things have changed.
I didn't think the
master ever would.
Yahiko...
[ZENKO gasps]
It hurts.
Zenko!
Stop! Now!
[FOX] Oh, Haruitsuki.
The things I hear.
[ABENO]
Please.
[ASHIYA]
Oh, no.
This is what it feels like
to be possessed.
Like I said... Heh.
Lots of rumors floating
around about you.
Is it true that you wanted
to succeed Aoi so badly...
...you killed for the job?
[ASHIYA]
So I was right.
You and the fox
do know each other.
[ABENO]
Yeah.
[ASHIYA]
Cool.
What about dogs
and monkeys and stuff?
You friends with
anything like that?
[ABENO]
Shut up.
I'm not Doctor Doolittle.