You're those two
clowns from the other day.
[ABENO] Sorry if we caused
you any inconvenience.
You've got some kinda nerve.
Anyone who makes my
daughter cry like that
oughta have their
face rearranged.
Oh, please don't hurt us!
We're only here because she
called and asked us to come.
[ZENKO'S DAD]
She called you?!
I'll delete her
number right now, sir!
[ZENKO]
You don't have to do that.
I really appreciate you
coming on such short notice.
Make yourselves at home.
Forgive the intrusion.
I can't believe you're letting
them back into our home!
Listen, Dad.
If you keep insisting on
being rude to my new friends,
Mom is gonna hear
about everything.
[ABENO]
So how is Yahiko?
[ZENKO] Well, he's definitely
got a lot of energy.
[YAHIKO] Haruitsuki,
will you help me, please?
I got stuck back here, somehow!
[ZENKO] I came home from
school and he was like this.
It is pretty common
for yokai to grow
when they're feeling
upset about something.
I wasn't upset!
I had just eaten some rakugan ,
and then laid down in the
sun to take a nice long nap,
and when I woke up
I was gigantic!
Now I can't get back to normal.
Did you do anything
else before your nap?
Like what?
Scavenge for food?
You take that back!
I had rakugan and some potatoes!
And I did not "scavenge" for
them, thank you very much!
What potatoes?
[YAHIKO] The potatoes
that I snitched earlier.
You think that sounds better?
It's a whole lot
worse if you ask me!
Yahiko, are these the potatoes
you were talking about?
I almost didn't see Fuzzy there.
It's kinda like he's
semi-transparent.
You can't see him
as well as us?
Well, I can see
Yahiko very clearly.
But Fuzzy's "fuzzy."
They smell like
the same ones to me.
Apparently, my dad ate some
of these for lunch as well.
But he's his usual self.
Whoa.
Honestly, I think the smell
would kill my appetite.
[ASHIYA]
Ugh!
Man, they stink!
That's gotta be one of the
worst things I've ever smelled
in my life!
It's not that bad to me.
Ooh. I love the smell.
Can I have another one?
No, you can't.
[YAHIKO]
Hey, Haruitsuki.
I guess I didn't notice before.
But they smell...
...kinda like yokai to me.
[YAHIKO] It's from the
dirt on the potatoes.
From the dirt?
My mom grew them
herself on a nearby farm
that she shares with one
of our parishioners.
Yeah?
Then we should probably
go there and check things out
for ourselves.
Don't you think?
That's fine, just close the
damn bag already, would ya?
I don't like the idea
of you going anywhere
with these guys.
I'm serious, young lady.
Do you hear me?
Of course I can hear you.
And we're going to the farm.
Ya know, I get
a real strong feeling
that your dad actually hates us.
Well, it would certainly be
a stretch to say he likes us.
I'm really sorry
about all of this.
For bothering you with
whatever's going on with Yahiko.
And for my dad being
a total jerk to you.
Look. We understand.
Your dad's just
worried about you
like any regular
dad would be.
And it's only because
he truly loves you.
So let's go.
You're not bothering us.
We wanna help
you out with Yahiko.
He's right.
And I'm sorry that Yahiko
is causing you trouble.
Taking care of it is
my responsibility.
We are all the
same age, right?
Or are you really an adult?
Well, I'm more of
an adult than you.
[ASHIYA] Oh, yeah, you think
I'm like a five-year-old!
[ZENKO]
I'm glad they're here.
Really? Is that so?
That's enough.
'Kay.
[ZENKO] I just hope that Dad
eventually starts warming up
to them someday.
[ASHIYA]
So this is your mom's farm?
[ZENKO]
Mm-hmm.
[ASHIYA]
It's so stinky.
How can any of the neighbors
put up with the stench?
[ABENO] We're probably
the only ones who see
or smell it like this.
[ASHIYA]
Just us?
[gasps]
Which means...
[ABENO]
Yep. I sense a yokai in there.
Then let's go in and find it.
You think your nose
will be able to handle it?
I'm cool.
I'll just hold my breath!
That's not a workable strategy.
It doesn't seem to
bother me as much.
So I guess that means
it's all up to me
to take care of this one.
[ABENO]
Not gonna happen.
What's Fuzzy doing?
Fuzzy?
[gasps] Fuzzy!
You're getting mud all
over your beautiful fur!
[ASHIYA]
You're covered in it!
This means I'll have
to bathe you later! Aww...
And that's not the only thing.
I think he's getting bigger.
[ASHIYA yelps]
How did he get so heavy?
He'll crush me!
Looks like it's a
fairly safe assumption
that the mud is what made
Yahiko get so big, too.
How can we make him
cuddle-sized again?
Will you please wait around
here with the hairball?
[ZENKO]
Mm-hmm.
[ABENO]
All right, Ashiya, let's go.
Okay.
[ASHIYA coughing]
It stinks! So bad!
Cut it out!
The stench is just so much
worse than it was out there.
[coughing]
[ABENO]
The stench was enough.
Now I have the most annoying
soundtrack to go with it.
[pounding noise]
Do you hear that?
[pounding continues]
[NOBOU yowling]
It hurts!
He's hitting himself?
Hey, stop that!
You'll kill yourself if you
keep bashing your face in
with that rock!
[NOBOU]
A human?
Are you trying to kill yourself?
[NOBOU] Don't jump to
conclusions like that!
You got the wrong idea!
Anyway, that's not a rock!
[ABENO]
It's a potato.
Potatoes again?
[NOBOU] We are on a
potato farm, you know.
Well, it still
doesn't make sense!
[NOBOU] Oh, dear.
It seems I've been scolded.
But that's quite all right!
It's been so long since
I've spoken a word to anybody!
And my very first time
to speak with a human!
Please allow me
to introduce myself.
My name is Nobou,
at your service.
And who might you gentlemen be?
My name's Abeno.
From the Mononokean.
I'm his assistant, Ashiya.
[NOBOU gasps]
The Mononokean?
So the rumors are true?
Rumors?
[NOBOU] That you're
the yokai kidnappers!
You entice yokai
over and over again
and drag them
to the Underworld!
Not exactly.
We exorcise yokai .
But... You're not
entirely wrong.
It depends on your perspective.
[NOBOU]
So you are kidnappers?
We have never kidnapped anybody!
I hope they're okay in there.
[NOBOU] I see, you just
call it something else,
but it's basically kidnapping.
[ASHIYA] No, it's not
anything like that at all!
[NOBOU] I don't care
what you call it.
I'll go to the Underworld!
As long as you get me out
of this place, I'm happy!
I've been stuck here
as long as I can remember.
No matter what I try,
I can't seem to escape!
I'd do anything if
I could just leave!
Oh, dear.
[ASHIYA]
Ugh! It stinks!
[ABENO] Nobou, do you know
what the deal is with this mud?
[NOBOU]
I don't know the reason why,
but it just started welling
up from the ground one day
without any warning.
When I try to walk through it.
I grow more and more
depressed and despondent,
and I lose every bit
of energy I have in me.
Eventually, I'm too
tired to even move.
[ASHIYA]
Nobou!
[NOBOU] I become completely
enveloped in smoke
and I'm trapped in
a waking nightmare.
A phantasmagoria.
Next thing,
I find myself back here.
You have visions?
[NOBOU] In order to stop
seeing such things.
I tried to erase my memory
by hitting myself in the head.
That's what you were
doing with the potato?
[NOBOU] I've tried practically
everything by this point,
and I'd given up
all hope of escape.
But if you send me
to the Underworld,
I will finally have the
freedom that I've been
so desperately longing for.
Come, Mononokean!
Send me to the Underworld
as quickly as you can!
I can't right now. I'm sorry.
[NOBOU]
Oh, dear.
It's happening again.
We've gotta do something!
The smell is killing me.
I can't stay focused enough
to open up a portal.
[coughing]
So. Our first priority is
getting you out of this field
to somewhere that I can actually
think a little more clearly.
[NOBOU] But I told you
what happens when I walk
through the mud!
Yes, I remember.
[ASHIYA]
Heave-ho.
[ASHIYA] You should be fine if
you're not actually touching it.
[NOBOU laughing]
[ASHIYA]
Okay, here we go!
[NOBOU]
Thank you!
[ASHIYA coughs]
[NOBOU] We're still in
the thick of the smoke.
You're right.
It doesn't make any
kind of sense to me.
[ABENO] I was already having
trouble with the horrible smell.
And now, the smoke
has gotten so dense
I can't see my hand
in front of my face.
[ASHIYA]
Are we lost?
I was using the hairball's
presence to navigate.
But I can't pick it up anymore.
Don't tell me we're
stuck in here now, too!
[ABENO]
There's no other choice.
All right, Nobou.
Looks like I'm gonna have
to try to exorcise you here.
[NOBOU]
I don't know.
The whole thing is
making me really nervous!
Can you summon a portal?
I mean, the smell is even
more pungent right here.
And it would probably be
easier if we were somewhere
with less smoke,
don't you think?
What I really think...
[ASHIYA]
Huh?
[ABENO] ...is you should shut up
for at least 30 seconds.
Okay, sorry.
[ASHIYA]
Thirty seconds.
[coughs]
[ASHIYA]
He's gonna kill me for that!
[ASHIYA] Ah! I didn't
mean to do it, I swear!
Wait... a scarecrow?
[ASHIYA gasps]
Where am I?
[NOBOU] Did you see how hard
I was working, old chum?
I am in rare form today!
[ASHIYA]
Nobou!
Uh... Did I accidentally
let go of you?
Sorry 'bout that.
[NOBOU] You can tell
me you're impressed.
I can handle the compliment.
[ASHIYA]
Hold on...
[NOBOU]
Yes, I even surprised myself!
[ASHIYA]
Is this the phantasmagoria
he was talking about?
[NOBOU]
...can go a long way!
And you're such a good friend.
Hey, Nobou, can you
even hear me right now?
[NOBOU]
We make a great team, don't we?
Ready to protect the rice
from scavengers and invaders
without ever tiring
or complaining.
[NOBOU] What came next happened
in the blink of an eye.
I wanted to carry my
friend away from the flames
where he'd be safe.
But I was overwhelmed
by the heat
and utterly frozen by my fear.
Every time I
revisit this memory,
this waking nightmare...
It's like I'm right back in the
middle of the fire once again.
It's as if my old
friend is keeping me
from leaving this place.
I imagine it's because he
resents me for my inability
to save him that day.
[ASHIYA]
Nobou...
He's enormous now.
[NOBOU] I foolishly believed
that with your help,
I would finally be able
to escape this place.
That I would stop reliving
my horrible failure
over and over again.
But my friend
put a curse on me.
He couldn't forgive
my lack of action.
I just stood there
while he burned.
So he's bound me
here for all eternity.
[ASHIYA]
You're wrong!
You were trying to save him
the only way you could.
It's not your fault
he didn't make it!
[NOBOU]
That's kind of you.
But I failed him.
[ABENO] Well...
I think it was your fault.
Uh, wait. Do you mean that?
Definitely.
I apologize, Nobou.
But due to the state
that you're in right now,
I'm afraid...
...I can't exorcise you.
[NOBOU]
Oh. I see.
I suppose this is my fate.
[ASHIYA] Abeno, you saw what
happened that day, didn't you?
Yes, I did.
Then could you bother telling us
what exactly Nobou did wrong?
I mean, he was in the
worst situation possible!
What could he have
done differently?
[ASHIYA]
Ow!
Ashiya.
What if it had been you instead?
If you had been in
Nobou's place that day,
scared, unable to
help your friend...
Do you think you could claim
you weren't responsible?
Listen up, Nobou.
It's not your old friend
that's binding you here.
If you want my take on it,
you're doing this yourself.
[NOBOU]
I am? What do you mean?
Don't you think it's possible
that you subconsciously
created all this mud and
smoke to keep yourself here?
You made it so you
could never run away.
So you couldn't leave
anybody behind again.
[NOBOU]
Oh, dear.
This is embarrassing.
What's happening to me?
Am I really crying?
That's why I can't exorcise you.
Because you don't
really want to leave.
But you can't
stay here anymore.
So you have to make a decision.
Do you understand?
You have to discover
the resolve inside yourself.
[NOBOU] If I do that,
you think I can leave?
[ABENO] All right, man,
it's time we got back to Zenko
and the hairball.
[ASHIYA]
What about him?
He's gonna have to stay
here until he can leave
on his own.
Don't you understand that
he's not able to do that?
That's the reason why he needed
our help in the first place!
If you can't walk,
drag yourself.
[NOBOU]
Huh?
Just keep moving.
Through all of this smoke.
Don't give up.
It's the only way outta here.
[phone chimes]
It's a text from Zenko
asking if we're okay.
She's worried.
[ABENO]
Tell her we're on our way back.
[ASHIYA]
Yeah, okay.
[ABENO]
Nobou.
Take all the time you need.
We'll be waiting for you.
[NOBOU] But if the mud
and smoke overtake me again,
it could take quite a long time
to get to the edge of the field.
[ABENO, ASHIYA]
We'll wait.
[ABENO]
Don't worry.
I promise I won't abandon you.
Come on, Ashiya.
[NOBOU]
You're leaving.
Before you go,
you realize you could
be waiting forever.
That I may never make it out.
Yet... You're still
willing to wait for me?
We are!
We'll be seeing ya!
[coughs]
It's so stinky.
[NOBOU]
My friend...
I shackled myself here
with all this mud and smoke
because I foolishly believed
that by remaining in that day,
I could somehow atone
for what I did.
However...
The time has come for
me to leave, my friend.
And once I'm gone,
I can never return.
[NOBOU]
I can't give up.
I must keep moving forward.
They are waiting for me.
I don't want them
to wait forever.
These will be the last
words I speak to you,
old friend.
Therefore I must tell
you what's been weighing
on my conscience
for far too long.
[NOBOU gasps]
[NOBOU] My dear friend, if I
had been more strong of heart.
If I had endured the
flames a bit longer.
If I had pulled a bit harder.
So many things I could've
done differently.
Maybe I could've been
able to save you that day.
But I did what I did,
and I lost you.
[sobs]
I ran away.
And though I've regretted
my actions these many years,
that is what led me to them.
For the first time,
I'm happy that I chose to run.
Because I feel this way,
I don't think I can truly
claim that I am your friend.
How could I be glad
about leaving you behind?
[sobs]
But know this.
Before tragedy struck
our field and destroyed
all that we had known,
I spent the happiest
days of my life
working in the hot
sun alongside you.
There is no joy that
could ever compare to it.
You gave me a gift for which
I am eternally grateful.
Thank you for being there.
Thank you for listening.
Thank you for understanding!
[NOBOU]
Goodbye...
...my dear old friend.
Goodbye.
[ZENKO] Nobou still hasn't
made it out of the farm.
Is Abeno asleep?
[ASHIYA] He doesn't want us
to talk to him so he can focus.
Focus? On what?
On summoning a portal
to the Underworld.
Smell's been getting in the way.
[ZENKO]
A portal to the Underworld?
Do you think you
should head home soon?
I bet your dad's worried sick.
No, it's okay.
He's gonna be super mad
at me, but I don't care.
I'll wait here with you.
[NOBOU]
Abeno! Ashiya!
Nobou!
[laughs] You made it!
[NOBOU grunts]
[NOBOU]
Oh, dear.
Well, that was a
little embarrassing.
I want you to know that
I owe my freedom to you.
I was finally able
to leave that place.
Because you said
that you'd wait for me.
[NOBOU crying]
You gave me the
courage to face my fears
and say goodbye
to my old friend!
[ASHIYA] It must have been
more painful for him
than any of us
could've imagined.
But his faith in
the promise we made...
...gave him the
strength to move on.
[ASHIYA] Thank you for
finding your resolve.
And thank you
for believing in yourself.
[NOBOU] No, thank you
for helping me find it
and for waiting for me.
Look at the farm.
[ABENO] Nobou, I'm glad
to see you've made it through.
[NOBOU]
Thank you, Abeno.
[crying]
If I may ask this
of you one last time...
...will you grant my wish
and send me to the Underworld?
[ABENO]
Of course I will.
[ZENKO] It really is a
portal to the Underworld.
[NOBOU]
My dear friend.
I will cherish the memories
of those wonderful days
we spent together.
I will take that happiness
and pain with me
to the Underworld.
You will be in my
thoughts for all eternity.
[NOBOU] Thank you
for bidding me farewell!
Thank you!
[NOBOU] Thank you,
my most treasured friend.
[ASHIYA] Zenko's dad definitely
has the wrong idea about me.
But Abeno...
With his blond hair, good looks,
and those eyes that bore
right through your soul,
he seems way more dangerous.
[ABENO]
Now, who's dangerous?
[ASHIYA gasps]
Hold on!
How long have you
been standing there?
[ABENO]
Long enough.