[ASHIYA]
This is it.
Today's the day.
I'm actually gonna make it.
Come on. You've got this.
[ASHIYA sighs]
[ASHIYA] Okay, on second
thought, maybe not.
Get it together, man.
Yokai aren't real.
Just a story made up
for kids. Right?
At least that's what
I used to tell myself.
[ASHIYA]
Several days ago...
[ASHIYA'S MOM] Hanae, sweetie,
can you do me a favor?
[ASHIYA]
What is it?
Do you mind stopping by
the store and picking up
a few things for dinner tonight?
Yeah, sure.
[ASHIYA'S MOM]
Thanks.
Back-to-school season's
got me super busy.
Voilà!
These are for you.
For being such a good son.
Let's call it a
"proud mother's bouquet."
[ASHIYA] Do you have to express
everything with flowers?
[ASHIYA] Bell peppers.
Eggs. Baby carrots.
Cool, that's everything
on the list.
[gasps]
[ASHIYA]
Just a stuffed animal.
Some kid must've dropped it.
Now you'll be easier
for your owner to find,
and no one else'll step on ya.
I did a good deed!
Am I ready for high school
or am I ready for high school?
Talk about mature!
Hey, what the--?
[ASHIYA growls]
Hey... Uh... Stop!
[grunting]
Get offa me!
What is this thing?
[ASHIYA]
I'm home.
How did it go?
I thought you'd be back before--
Honey, you look awful.
Is everything all right?
Not by a long shot.
I can't get whatever
this is off of me.
[ASHIYA'S MOM]
What are you talking about?
This thing. It's stuck.
Hm? Do you mean your hood?
[ASHIYA'S MOM]
Crocuses.
In the language of flowers,
they say, "I believe you,
but I'm a bit concerned."
[ASHIYA]
She can't see it?
What's wrong with me?
I have a headache,
I'm nauseous, crazy tired,
so off-balance it's all I can
do to walk in a straight line.
And as far as I can tell,
I'm the only one that
can see this thing.
Almost there.
Just a little farther.
[FEMALE STUDENT 1D gasps]
Ah, that's cold!
I'm wearing an ice pack?
[NURSE 1A]
Feeling better?
Wait, am I...
in the nurse's office?
Oh. Yes, you collapsed at
the front gate this morning.
What? I should get to class!
Now, now.
Don't get all worked up.
School's over for the day.
[ASHIYA]
Say wha--?
[ASHIYA] Way to start
things off on the right foot.
I spent my first day of
high school unconscious.
To make matters worse,
I still feel like crap.
Clearly, the common
denominator here...
...is this stupid fuzz ball!
I get it, okay?
Yokai are real!
--[ASHIYA] Get off!
--[STUDENTS gasp]
--[ASHIYA] Leave me alone!
--Um, what exactly is he doing?
I don't know.
Maybe we should hang back.
[ASHIYA]
Day two.
[ASHIYA] First time I've
actually cleared the gate.
Today I turn over a new leaf.
My life as a high
school student begins.
[STUDENTS gasp]
[MALE STUDENT 1E]
Man down! Man down!
[MALE STUDENT 1D]
Get him to the nurse's office!
[ASHIYA]
Day three.
[FEMALE STUDENT 1G]
Ah! Oh, no! He's dead!
[MALE STUDENT 1F]
Somebody call the nurse!
[ASHIYA]
Day four.
[MALE TEACHER 1A]
You okay, kid? Need the nurse?
[ASHIYA]
Day five.
You're really
not looking so hot.
Meh. It's nothing.
I'll be all right.
It could be anemia.
Used to make me pass out all the
time when I was a little girl.
I think it's hereditary.
Sure. See you tonight, Mom.
[ASHIYA'S MOM] I'll make an
arrangement of red gardenias!
'Kay? In flower-speak, they
mean "perseverance!"
I believe in you!
[ASHIYA] Perseverance.
That's the key.
Don't give up. Keep going.
You've got this.
[ASHIYA] Just a little bit
farther and I'll be in class.
Now, my life as a high school
student will finally--
[groans]
[ASHIYA]
This is ridiculous.
My whole high school experience
has been in the nurse's office!
Ever since this
fuzz ball showed up,
I've been getting
worse and worse.
Meanwhile it's getting
bigger by the day.
Obviously it's feeding on me.
Unless I get rid of it
somehow, I'll end up dead!
No!
I won't be taken down
by some cute little yokai !
[ASHIYA]
Look at me!
I haven't made any friends yet.
That's pathetic.
I don't want to die a loser!
Screw this!
Whoa...
Ugh! You made me
tear the bulletin--
Exorcists? Seriously?
I can't tell if this is
real, but you never know.
Odds are I'm walking into
someone's idea of a joke.
I'll end up a laughingstock.
But if there's even
a remote possibility
of shaking this thing...
I'll take my chances,
thank you very much.
Perseverance, right?
[ABENO]
Yes? Who is it?
[ASHIYA]
They picked up!
Um, can I talk to Abeno?
[ABENO]
Speaking.
Uh, hey.
So I stumbled across
your help wanted poster.
[ABENO]
Interesting.
You could actually see it?
Bit of a long shot on my part.
It was kind
of an accident.
[ABENO] Can you come in
for an interview right away?
[ASHIYA]
When?
[ABENO]
The sooner the better.
Where are you?
Oh, um, the nurse's office.
[ABENO] Fine. That'll work.
Open the door.
[ASHIYA]
Okay.
Where do I go from there?
[ABENO]
You'll see.
[ASHIYA]
What?
[ASHIYA] Is he already
waiting outside?
[ABENO] Come in and
take a seat over there.
[ABENO]
Something wrong?
[ASHIYA]
Uh...
No?
Whoa! The fuzz ball
totally shrank!
[ABENO]
I don't have all day.
Take off your shoes.
Right!
[ASHIYA] Has the nurse's office
always been next to a tearoom?
Here you go.
So, like, are you a...?
Indeed.
I am the master
of this Mononokean.
Haruitski Abeno.
So, when will you
be able to start?
[ASHIYA]
Huh?
[sighs]
Guess you'll have to do.
A bit scrawnier than I'd like,
but the only one
who answered my ad.
Actually, though...
I'm not here looking for work.
I was hoping you
could help me out.
Wait. You need my help?
This weird fuzzy thing's
latched on to my back;
it's caused me
nothing but problems!
I saw your post and thought
maybe you could do an exorcism!
That is, if this is for real.
I mean, that is the kind
of thing you do, right?
[ABENO]
Of course. Consider it done.
Oh, that'd be awesome!
I've been living a nightmare!
Wow. You actually
thought I was serious.
Get out and stop
wasting my time.
Huh?!
Hold on a minute!
Will you let go of me?
There's gotta be
something you can do!
C'mon, I'm begging!
I only let you in
here because I thought
you were looking for work!
If it's an exorcism
you're after,
I'm afraid you'll just
have to wait your turn!
How long are we talking about?
You have other
customers or something?
About ten days.
Ten days?
If that's not good enough
for you, do something
about it yourself.
[ASHIYA]
No, no. It's fine. I'll wait.
[ASHIYA] Will I even
be alive in ten days?
Very well.
Tell me who you are and I can
put you on the waiting list.
[ASHIYA]
Hanae Ashiya.
That's your name?
[ABENO]
Ashiya? Really?
There some kind of problem?
What's the big deal?
[ABENO]
Fine.
I'll do the exorcism now.
You mean I won't have to wait?
I changed my mind.
Now, step outside, please.
I'll be right behind you.
Yeah. Sure thing.
There's no door.
[ABENO]
Look down.
It's at your feet.
[ASHIYA]
Really? Uh...
Could someone tell me what's
going on here, please?
[ASHIYA]
What the--?
How am I on the roof?!
[ABENO]
Keep your voice down.
It's annoying.
But the nurse's office
is on the first floor,
and now we're way up here.
I don't know about you,
but my head's spinning.
[gasping]
It's getting... bigger!
Yes it is.
[ASHIYA]
I can't take this anymore!
Please, you've got to make
it go away, Abeno!
I'll be a dead man
in a matter of hours
if this giant marshmallow
sticks around much longer!
You're not helping.
Stop kicking it and shut up.
[ASHIYA yells]
[ASHIYA coughing]
[ASHIYA]
What's that about?
Why does he look so grim
all of a sudden?
Is that some sort
of exorcism tool?
Maybe...
...a deadly spell?
Oh, man.
Inflating one of these is
always harder than you think.
[ASHIYA]
Are you kidding?!
What's a beach ball got to do
with exorcising this thing?
What are talking about?
I'm playing.
[growling]
[ASHIYA] Now you're
just messing with me!
[ASHIYA]
That's it! I'm done!
If you don't want to help, fine,
but you don't have to be a jerk!
Just so you know,
kicking a guy while he's down
isn't a nice thing to do!
Super not cool!
I knew it.
You're exactly like the others.
What?
[ABENO]
Look, man.
Just so you know...
It's no skin off
my nose if you die.
I don't do this for people.