[FEMALE STUDENT 2A]
Sit with me at lunch?
[FEMALE STUDENT 2B]
Sure!
[ASHIYA] Can't believe he
slept all the way through
fourth period.
Oh, hey. You're awake.
It's lunchtime.
Don't try to play it all cool!
You knew were we classmates
and didn't say squat!
Yeah? So?
[ASHIYA]
You might've clued me in.
Huh?
Is that a yokai ?
'Kay. So I'm guessing I
can see all of them now.
You gonna exorcise
it now or later?
Not unless someone hires me to.
Wouldn't stay in
business very long
if I ran around
doing it for free.
Yeah, but I thought
you said yokai belong
in the Underworld.
We can't just leave him here.
He'll wander the earth forever.
It isn't right to
turn a blind eye.
[gasps]
I hired you to
make life easier.
That means you ignore
any yokai you come across
unless I expressly
say otherwise, got it?
Right. Moving on.
Go buy me some tea
and cod roe rice balls.
[ASHIYA]
So I'm his errand boy?
[ASHIYA] Why can't he
get his own lunch?
Whatever. If it
pays off my debt, fine.
[ASHIYA]
Ugh. No...
Aw, man. Should've gone
to the convenience store.
[FEMALE STUDENT 2C gasps]
You all right?
Is something the matter?
My leg just went numb.
It won't move.
[FEMALE STUDENT 2E]
Should we get the nurse?
[FEMALE STUDENT 2D]
You roll your ankle?
[FEMALE STUDENT 2C]
No. But it hurts.
[ABENO] Ignore any yokai
you come across.
[MALE STUDENT 2A]
She okay?
[FEMALE STUDENT 2D]
No. She can't move her leg.
[MALE STUDENT 2B] Whoa!
We should call an ambulance!
[ASHIYA]
Dang it.
I can't ignore this!
What the--?
I can move it.
How did you--?
You should be good
from here on out, I think.
But stop by the nurse's
just in case.
[FEMALE STUDENT 2C]
Uh...
Sure thing, thanks.
[MALE STUDENT 2A]
What happened?
This guy fixed her leg using
nothing but his hand!
Seriously? He's a healer!
Wow!
Someone in our school has
magical healing powers!
[ASHIYA] I want nothing
to do with yokai ,
but how am I supposed to
pretend they're not around?
[ASHIYA]
Why do I have the chills?
I know this feeling.
It's like when the
fuzz ball latched onto me.
Except this is way
more... terrifying.
[ANT screams]
The heck is that noise?!
[screaming continues]
[ASHIYA] Am I the only
one who hears it?
[ANTS chittering]
[ABENO]
By all means, take your time.
[ASHIYA screams]
[FEMALE STUDENT 2I]
What's up with him?
[FEMALE STUDENT 2H]
No idea.
That's loud. Jeez.
Abeno.
[ASHIYA whimpering]
[ASHIYA]
Please! You have to help me!
What did I tell you
not ten minutes ago?!
What the hell are you doing?!
Remember when I said I
hired you to make life easier?
[ASHIYA]
I know! I'm sorry!
Unbelievable!
Of all the things to get
yourself possessed by...
Excuse us, ladies.
[FEMALE STUDENT 2I]
Oh, but...
Mononokean, come!
[rattling noise]
[ASHIYA gasps]
[ASHIYA]
What the--? Knock it off!
You're choking me!
[ABENO]
Son of a--
Deal with it!
Hey! Listen!
I need you to get your
fingertips inside the door!
Wait, seriously?
That's it?
[ANTS chittering]
[grunting]
[ASHIYA]
It worked!
Go in. While you can.
It's the tearoom.
The same one from yesterday!
[ANTS chittering]
Oh. All right.
[ABENO]
Door's closing.
Move it or lose it.
That was a close one.
You're not out of
the woods yet, genius.
The second you set foot
outside this room,
they'll dog-pile you again.
Aw, c'mon!
But I was finally getting to be
a normal high school student!
[ABENO]
Take off your shoes.
[ASHIYA]
Hang on...
Summon that sliding door again.
That'll lead 'em to
the Underworld, won't it?
--Not possible.
--[ASHIYA] How come?
Well, not that it's
any of your business,
but I'm only able to open
the door to the Underworld
twice a day.
So there's nothing we can do?
[ABENO]
What do you want from me?
They're a swarm.
It'd take days to
exorcise all of them.
I only have so much strength.
[ASHIYA] Those things are gonna
chase me the rest of my life?
[ABENO]
Calm down.
We have options.
So there's hope?
[ABENO] They pack more of
a wallop than you'd expect,
small as they are.
They're young,
but they're strong.
Like worker ants.
[ASHIYA] Does that mean
there's like a "queen ant"
calling the shots?
Exactly.
And they were trying you to
take you to the big boss's nest.
Give it something to feed on.
[ASHIYA]
Feed?
Maybe. Just an educated guess.
I won't know what
the boss yokai wants
till I meet it face-to-face.
I need you to
stay here for now.
If you get eaten, I'll be SOL.
I'm not about to lose
the money you owe me.
[ASHIYA]
Whoa! Wait a minute!
[ABENO]
Calm down.
Lunch will have to wait.
No, no!
That isn't it!
You're gonna try to exorcise
the boss yokai all by yourself?
[ABENO] You ever want to leave
this room again, I have to.
[ASHIYA]
I don't think you should.
What?
Are you listening to me?
It's your only way out!
[ASHIYA]
But what if you get eaten?
I could never forgive myself
if you died because of me!
I'd have to transfer
to a whole other school!
[ABENO]
He's scared out of his mind.
Well... all things considered,
I can't blame him.
He's not like me.
Don't go.
Look, I've been doing
this kinda stuff for years.
You don't have to worry
about me; take my word for it.
I'm different than
you are, okay?
I'll get you when it's over.
Oh, and just so you're aware,
I'm adding this to your debt.
[ASHIYA]
Wait! Let me go with you!
Please! At best,
you'd be yokai bait!
Fine, then. Use me as bait.
What?
[ASHIYA]
I can distract the little ones
while you try to find the boss.
That's a solid plan, right?
[ABENO] It would be, if you
weren't shaking like a leaf.
What? I can't be scared?
You're staying.
[ASHIYA] Come on, like you
aren't petrified at the idea
of going it alone.
'Scuse me?
[ASHIYA]
Look, I get it.
You're a professional.
You're awesome, blah blah blah.
But you're scared.
We're in the same grade.
We've got the same lanky build.
We can both see yokai .
What I'm trying to say is
we have a lot more in
common than you might think.
And besides, this whole
mess is my fault, right?
I have a responsibility.
I can't let you
fix it on your own.
I can help you! Trust me!
[ABENO]
Persuasive.
Sure, why not?
This can be your first job.
You wanna be bait?
Go ahead. Be bait.
[ASHIYA gasps]
Thanks!
[ABENO] Go out there
and give 'em a nibble.
[ASHIYA]
What?!
[ANT chitters]
[BIG BOSS SCREE groans]
[BIG BOSS SCREE]
Ki ki ki ki...
Ah, even more, great.
They're all staring at me.
[ABENO]
Go on, do your thing.
[ASHIYA]
Hey! Stop pushing me!
[ABENO]
You're the bait.
We've had this discussion.
We agreed you're not actually
gonna let them eat me, right?
[ABENO]
Uh, yeah. Sure. Whatever.
At least try to convince me!
If they get me, it's on you.
I'll come back as a yokai
and make your life miserable!
Till I exorcise you.
Today.
Hey! I'm going, all right?
[ABENO]
Here, take this.
Wear it around your neck.
Is it some kind of charm?
Oh!
As long as I've got it on,
the yokai won't attack.
Not how it works
at all, actually.
Uh...!
If you get eaten, it'll be
unfortunate but I'll live.
[ASHIYA]
Hey!
That I can't do without, though.
So, yeah.
Wait, then you're...?
You're saying that as
long as I'm wearing this,
you have an incentive
to keep me safe!
You really do care if I'm eaten!
[ABENO sighs]
--Shut up!
--[ASHIYA grunts]
[ASHIYA yelps]
[ABENO]
Damn it.
[ASHIYA]
Abeno!
[ANT chittering]
[ANTS chittering]
[BIG BOSS SCREE]
Oh, dear.
A human child is far from ideal,
but I have little choice.
Ki!
Ki ki ki ki ki!
Oh, crap!
Wait, where's Abeno?
I... He was just...
[ANTS chittering]
[ASHIYA gasps]
They've eaten him!
Get off, fun's over!
Whoa! You're alive?
What's the point
of making me the bait
if you let
yourself get caught?
[ABENO]
I screwed up, okay?
I thought they were
only after you.
Whatever.
Look! We have a bigger problem!
[BIG BOSS SCREE]
Two human children?
Incredible.
You can see us?
Hear us?
Extraordinary.
Are you the yokai these
smaller ones answer to?
I am.
And it seems they've brought
me something unusual.
If you can see yokai ,
might I ask,
do you know of
one in particular?
He helps other yokai .
Sends them to the Underworld.
He is known as the
Master of the Mononokean.
[ASHIYA]
Wait a second.
Didn't Abeno call himself that?
I swear he did.
I imagine you have a
favor you'd like to ask him?
Indeed, but forgive me.
There's no point relaying
it to a human.
[ABENO] Mononokean Master,
Haruitsuki Abeno,
requesting a portal
to the Underworld.
[ASHIYA]
What the--?
[BIG BOSS SCREE]
Ki ki ki?
I'm as close as
you're gonna get.
You want something,
I suggest you talk.
I wasn't expecting a human.
How very surprising.
I confess to feeling
a trifle uneasy,
but if you really
are the master...
I humbly ask you, please
send us to the Underworld.
Fine, but there's a problem.
[BIG BOSS SCREE]
Yes.
For now, I ask you
send the little ones.
As for me...
We'll get to that.
[ANTS chittering]
[ASHIYA]
Ew...
[ABENO]
Hey, careful.
You missed one of 'em.
[ASHIYA]
There's more?
Um, Big Boss Scree?
How many of these
things are there?
[BIG BOSS SCREE]
Ki ki ki!
Don't call me that.
I sense no others.
[ASHIYA]
Okay. That's all of them.
[sigh]
We're finally finished.
That just leaves Big
Boss Sc-- um, the big boss.
[BIG BOSS SCREE]
Oh.
I'm afraid you don't understand.
[ASHIYA]
Huh?
What'd you close it for?
We're not done yet!
[BIG BOSS SCREE]
Child, please.
Look closely at my body.
[ASHIYA]
Is something wrong with it?
My roots have grown deep.
I'm anchored to this world.
[ASHIYA]
Roots?
[ABENO]
They're called parasite shrubs.
They attach themselves
to yokai and grow
by draining their strength.
The deeper they are,
the weaker the host.
Cursed, the Underworld calls it.
Here, we'd say an
incurable disease.
I've accepted my fate.
So long as the little ones
made it to the Underworld.
My only wish was to
see my children thrive
before I withered away.
I am most grateful
for your help.
Now I may die in peace.
[ASHIYA] Do the little ones know
you're not coming with them?
[BIG BOSS SCREE]
No.
I didn't want to
worry them unduly.
[ASHIYA]
Uh-uh.
No! You're going!
Even if I have to cut
these roots myself!
What? Ah!
Don't be stupid!
They're not normal roots!
Chop 'em off, they
grow back instantly!
Then I'll find another way!
I'm not just gonna stand
there and let him die!
[ABENO] What's gotten
into him all of a sudden?
He was scared out
of his mind before.
You can't abandon your children.
[BIG BOSS SCREE]
Ki?
You know they'll
be waiting for you
in the Underworld.
For crying out loud,
you didn't even give them
a proper goodbye!
You wanna leave them
hanging like that?
Child, do not speak as
though you understand me.
The little ones were
my reason for living.
I'd tear myself limb from
limb to be with them.
Endure anything without
a second thought.
Alas, it is not possible
for me to join them.
I must be content with
seeing them on their way.
Such is my fate.
Though, if I had one more wish,
it would be to be their guardian
until they are big enough
to fend for themselves.
But that hope I must abandon.
But you...
[ASHIYA]
Now what?
[ABENO]
If you'd really endure anything,
there might be a way
to get you there.
It's a long shot, though.
Whoa. What is that?
Think of it as a pill.
Swallow it and the parasite
shrub will be weakened.
Huh?
Could you maybe have said
something about this before?
The catch is, the
agony it'll cause you
is beyond imagination.
Pain so great, some people
have even died from it.
[ABENO]
Still interested?
[BIG BOSS SCREE]
Ki.
Is it possible?
[BIG BOSS SCREE] I would be with
my children whatever the cost.
Until my body withers to dust.
Mononokean Master Abeno.
Please.
Send me to the Underworld!
Sure, if that's
what you really want.
[BIG BOSS SCREE groaning]
Ki! Ki! Ki!
[BIG BOSS SCREE]
Ki! It burns!
Ki! Ki ki ki ki!
[screaming continues]
He's more manageable
this way, I'll give you that.
Partially due to
the medicine, of course.
But also because the
anxiety that made him grow
so large in the
first place is gone.
Now...
Either he'll wake up
or he won't.
Depends on how strong he is.
Big Boss Scree!
--You're okay! Thank goodness!
--[yelling]
Ashiya! Knock it off!
Oh! I'm sorry!
[ABENO]
He's strong enough to scream.
I'm impressed.
Forgive the inconvenience.
My children are worried.
I should be getting
on my way now.
Can you move on your own, or...?
I'll take a little while,
but I'll be fine.
[ABENO]
They waited.
Been right here
this whole time.
Glad you didn't give up?
[ANTS chittering]
Well, what do you know?
Very glad.
Very glad indeed.
[BIG BOSS SCREE] I cannot
express my gratitude enough.
You are a hero, my friend.
The name Abeno will ring far
and wide in the Underworld!
[ABENO] I hope not!
I'm swamped as it is!
Besides...
I've done absolutely nothing
to earn your gratitude.
At the end of the day all
I did was give you a pill,
but it was your strength
that did the heavy lifting.
I'm the Mononokean Master.
I should've been
able to do more.
Forgive me.
I needed help.
That's what you gave me.
So thank you.
You've done well.
Time to go, little ones.
Let's be on our way.
[ASHIYA]
Wait! I didn't...
I owe you an apology!
[BIG BOSS SCREE]
Hm?
[ASHIYA] It was wrong
of me to talk to you
the way I did.
I shouldn't have
questioned your devotion.
I shouldn't have been so quick
to want to chop off your roots.
[BIG BOSS SCREE]
Hey! That's enough!
Hang on.
You were going on what you knew.
I was way too harsh.
I had no right to call you out.
I'm sorry.
[BIG BOSS SCREE]
Ki ki ki.
If you hadn't said what you did,
I might not be here.
Ki ki ki.
Oh, yeah, right.
There's an apothecary in the
Underworld called Kiyakudo.
The master's a bit
on the eccentric side,
but you should visit
it while you're there.
It's definitely
worth the journey.
[BIG BOSS SCREE]
A recommendation from you
is good enough for me.
Ki ki ki!
Well, friends.
We must part ways.
Farewell, Abeno!
Farewell, Ashiya!
Farewell.
Glad that's over with.
I feel like all I really did
was sit on the sidelines
and scream my head off.
Shut up, that's not true.
Look, if it hadn't been for you,
he wouldn't have even
asked for my help.
I would've never given
him the pill on my own.
It's because you got him
talking about his children
that I decided to do something.
I'm not the courageous type.
[ASHIYA]
Abeno!
Exorcising yokai 's a lot harder
than I thought it'd be.
I hope I do okay.
[ABENO]
No worries.
Let's just say I'm
managing my expectations.
[ASHIYA]
Gee, thanks!