["Headhunt" by Okamoto's]
[man singing in Japanese]
♪ ♪
AOBA: My tour of Ikebukuro
got sidetracked the other day,
and we never finished.
I thought if you're free,
we could try it again.
‐ That'd be irresponsible!
IZAYA: The Dollars don't expect
you to take responsibility.
‐ It's gonna be okay.
She's sleeping soundly now.
VARONA: [shouting in Russian]
It appears the bike
was marked somehow.
Or perhaps we can use it
as a lure for an ambush.
♪ ♪
MASAOMI: I'm about to tell you
the tale of a worthless guy.
It was exactly like
you told me, Izaya.
What?
Oh, right.
A high‐school dropout who
ran away from both his home
and from school.
[low‐key piano music]
♪ ♪
‐ Bullet trains sure are
amazing, aren't they?
‐ What do you think is
so amazing about 'em?
‐ The fact that they
go so straight.
‐ You're still as much
of a weirdo as ever, Saki.
SAKI: Am I?
I don't think I'm as bad as you.
‐ Am I really that weird?
‐ Yeah.
I know that you hate Izaya's
guts and all,
and yet you're running around
as his gofer.
It's totally twisted,
like some subway map.
Although I actually like that
about you.
‐ Uh...
You don't pull your punches when
it comes to sensitive stuff.
He doesn't have any way
to support himself,
so he's making ends meet
by being that
good‐for‐nothing's gofer.
He's a guy with
no real purpose‐‐
a guy with nothing
to offer the world.
♪ ♪
‐ [grunting]
[growling]
That goddamn fleabag.
He's wasting my time!
[growling]
MASAOMI: For some reason,
the guy still has a friend.
‐ Having a good morning, Mikado?
‐ Uh, Aoba, what's going on?
I thought we were supposed
to meet at 11:00.
‐ Yeah, I know.
But before we go meet Anri,
I had something important
I wanted to talk
to you about first.
‐ You could've just called my
cell if you wanted to talk.
Uh, hey, who gave you
my address?
‐ It's about the Dollars.
‐ Uh?
‐ But not here.
Let's go somewhere else.
‐ [stammering]
‐ If you need a little time
to get changed,
we don't mind waiting for you.
‐ [exhales softly]
I wonder if you can still
call them friends,
even though you haven't
seen them for a long time.
Good morning!
Yay! Wait.
Figures that no one's around.
It's morning, after all.
Plus, my last login was probably
about a week ago.
I'm super sorry that I couldn't
be part of these chats
for such a long time.
Thanks to work, I've been
away with my girlfriend
for a lovey‐dovey rendezvous
in Tohoku.
How have you guys been?
Guess I'll dig through the logs
and see what you did
over the long weekend.
Yeah!
‐ I bet you're happy that you're
finally able to log on.
You're such a slave
to the Internet, Masaomi.
Masochist much?
‐ What's that supposed to mean?
‐ Well, you only meet up
with people online,
even when you can
see them in person.
‐ It's not that I won't see 'em.
It's that I can't.
Huh? What the...
‐ You're weird.
‐ What makes people friends
is spending time together,
isn't it?
Doing whatever together.
What the‐‐the logs up
to yesterday are gone.
Is this some kind of glitch?
Whatever.
See you later!
‐ [gasps]
Dr. Kishitani!
She's awake!
‐ [grunting]
[gentle piano music]
Hmm.
Mm‐hmm.
Good.
Your color's looking better.
You don't have any place
that hurts, do you?
Like a sore throat,
or a tummy‐ache,
or anything like that?
You're fine?
‐ Here.
‐ Hey, that smells tasty.
You've been a big help.
Thanks a lot for staying.
‐ [chuckles]
SHINRA: Come to think of it,
I forgot to tell Celty
about this girl.
After bringing Anri over,
Celty rushed out again,
like she was busy.
Something about
looking for someone...
hmm?
Shoo! Shoo!
‐ Uh...
♪ ♪
‐ If it's okay with you,
could you tell me your name?
‐ It's Akane.
‐ Akane, huh?
And your last name?
‐ [sighs softly]
‐ That's fine.
Are you all right
with telling me
what happened yesterday?
‐ [whimpers]
‐ Please tell me.
Why is that you wanted to make
the guy with sunglasses go away?
‐ Because he's a hitman.
‐ Uh‐huh?
‐ Uh‐huh.
Somebody told me about him
the other day.
He told me a hitman named Shizuo
was going to kill both my dad
and grandfather.
But since I can't go back
to my family,
I didn't know what
to do with myself.
‐ Then what about this?
Even I can tell that it's
been heavily modified.
‐ It was given to me
since I needed some way
to finish him off.
‐ Who did that?
‐ The same person who taught me
all sorts of things
when I first ran away from home.
‐ So just to clarify,
this person told you about
a hitman named Shizuo?
And he gave you this stun gun?
‐ Mm‐hmm.
‐ [gulps]
What was his name?
‐ He said to call him Izaya.
‐ [moans] Forgive me, Celty.
I might be beating you
to the afterlife.
What's with that gentle smile?
I've never seen it before.
‐ [laughs]
Just a misunderstanding, Akane.
‐ Huh?
‐ Izaya obviously has
the wrong idea about me.
I'm no hitman.
‐ Is that true?
‐ Yeah, it sure is.
Izaya's a friend of mine,
but we had a little falling out
a while back, that's all.
[chuckles]
‐ [laughs nervously]
‐ I'll go make up with him
right now.
[whistling]
‐ Hey!
That Izaya‐‐
is he tired of being alive
or something?
TOM: You really
kept it together.
That was some act.
I think you deserve the People's
Honor Award right now.
‐ Thanks.
I appreciate that.
And Tom, I've got a little favor
I'd like to ask you.
‐ What is it?
‐ If stuff goes down today
and I get arrested for murder
or worse,
then I want you to make sure
to tell our president
that I was fired yesterday.
Can you do that for me?
[elevator dings]
[growling]
That's twice you've
wasted my time.
So I'm gonna kill you twice!
[panting]
NAMIE: If a painfully obvious
ruse like this one
actually worked on him,
that Shizuo must be
quite the simpleton.
This was such a nuisance.
If he can't kill Shizuo
with a knife,
he could use poison
or something.
MASAOMI: The guy has a friend.
This friend may be
laughing or crying
or be in some kind of danger.
But all the guy ever does
is run away.
MIKADO: This place is creepy,
and it looks like
it's got roaches.
Let's go hang out
a hotel instead.
BOY: They're just roaches.
Eat 'em!
BOY: You eat one.
BOY: [laughing]
BOY: How much will
you pay if I do?
BOY: 300 yen.
BOY: Cheapskate.
BOY: I'm game.
BOY: Ugh, for real?
MIKADO: I know this place.
BOY: Hey, Aoba.
You're driving me crazy.
Can I smack him?
‐ Not yet.
‐ [giggling]
‐ Uhh!
[all laughing]
CELTY: Mikado?
Why is he here?
‐ I'm sorry, I had to step out
for a minute.
Anything happen?
‐ You completed your end
of assignment.
‐ Yes, it was piece of pie.
‐ This factory was abandoned
for some time.
Is now a hangout for
delinquent boys.
‐ Is hangout for
Black Rider, too.
I don't understand need to hide
from those kids, though.
‐ Is unclear.
‐ Shall we shoot?
‐ It was ineffective yesterday.
That thing is real monster.
If we use sniper rifle,
we'll give away position.
Could be fatal.
‐ Hmm?
‐ When it moves, I will
follow after.
Our target is the girl.
The monster may very well
lead us to her.
‐ Sounds as if you're
enjoying this, Verona.
‐ That is affirmative.
I am beginning to enjoy myself.
I am quite fond of Ikebukuro.
Half despair, half jealousy.
A dash of hope.
In other words, that's love.
‐ Last night, you were hanging
out on the Dollars' member site
asking around about some stuff,
weren't you?
You know, about the Dollar's
feud with the guys from Saitama.
‐ Uh, mm, I was looking into it.
Something was bugging me.
‐ I actually happen to know
everything about it.
‐ [gasps] Are you serious?
‐ Yeah, we're the ones
who did it.
‐ Huh?
‐ It wasn't a big deal, really.
Me and all the guys here...
[laughter]
Acting as members
of the Dollars,
we went over to Saitama
and attacked that gang.
‐ Uh, what's that?
‐ You know those guys calling
themselves the Toramaru?
Remember the other day?
They were chasing after us
in Kadota's van,
and that person
on the Black Bike.
‐ Uh, yeah, what about it?
‐ When we were down in Saitama,
we set a bunch of their bikes
on fire.
And while we were at it,
we sent about 20 of them
to the hospital.
‐ In other words, you tossed
a Molotov cocktail
into the parking lot where
they were hanging out at,
right, Aoba?
‐ Ah, but why?
‐ Funny thing is, we're not
just members of the Dollars.
We've also got another name.
‐ Another name?
‐ [chuckling]
I'm sure you must be familiar
with the Blue Squares.
‐ No way.
‐ I'm being honest with you.
Coming into contact
with a painting
is the same thing as meeting
the girl you're destined for.
‐ Yeah?
But in my eyes, you're more
of a masterpiece
than any painting could ever be.
WOMAN: What?!
Well, I think any man
who'd buy a painting like this
would be considered
God's gift to women.
‐ [laughs] You serious?
‐ It's as good as sold.
WOMAN: I really am.
CHIKAGE: Well, then...
‐ Yes?
Is there perhaps something
I can assist you with, sir?
‐ Yeah, there is, actually,
about this painting over here.
This lady's sort of in a bind
unless it's sold.
And so...
come on.
‐ What?
‐ It costs 1,280,000 yen.
If you don't have cash,
plastic's fine.
‐ Huh?
‐ Hey, get with the program.
She said that she'd be
in a bind and everything.
A real man wouldn't let her
go through that.
And you're standing
right there‐‐
a man who clearly has money.
You probably own this gallery,
don't you?
So naturally,
you've got capital.
‐ Well...
‐ You're supposed to use
your money for women.
Everyone knows that.
Now, if you call yourself a man,
go on ahead and buy this
painting and help the lady out.
‐ Now, now, sir.
Enough joking.
‐ Joking?
Did you think I was being funny?
When did I make you laugh, huh?
‐ Uh, please,
you don't have to.
‐ Hey, old man.
‐ Yes?
‐ It's obvious that young lady
over there is a hard worker.
So just where the hell
do you get off
glaring at her like that?
‐ [gasps]
[cell phone chimes]
‐ Found one?
Where are you?
What?
Which building?
I'll be coming back here
at some point
to check if you actually
bought that painting from her.
Are you serious?
Man, that's right out front.
‐ [moaning]
‐ So you sure about this?
‐ Yeah, it's a Dollars member
who kind of sticks out.
‐ Where is he right now?
‐ Well, that's the funny thing.
Just before you got here,
a girl called him over
and then took him inside
that building.
‐ Wha...?
‐ Well, we are talking
silkscreen here, after all.
At this size,
even with the frame,
the manufacturing cost would
only be 24,000 yen.
Don't get me wrong; I've got
respect for Suzie Yasuda,
so I wouldn't mind paying
a million yen for it.
But if I did, I'd have to have
some kind of proof
that at least 800,000 of it
was going to the creator.
It wouldn't sit well
with me otherwise.
‐ Uh, excuse me, sir?
‐ And the truth is that
your explanation of things
has a lot of holes in it‐‐
a lot!
You weren't able to describe
even 1% of Suzie's allure‐‐1!
Listen up‐‐what makes his work
so charming is his‐‐
‐ That's quite enough!
I can't believe you're
back here again!
Please leave at once!
There's no way you could
have known, since you're new,
but that customer's
been blacklisted.
So please, don't solicit
his patronage,
even if he does seem
like an easy mark.
‐ I'm sorry.
‐ [groaning]
I got to get out
of this business.
Ugh.
CHIKAGE: Him?
He doesn't look like one.
MAN: Well, from what I hear,
that's the kind of group
the Dollars is.
But I also hear that
a decent amount of our guys
got clobbered by one
of his buddies‐‐
a bastard named Kadota.
And that guy seems like
one of the top dogs
in the Dollars or something.
‐ Yeah?
Oh!
MAN: Hey, that's him.
That's Kadota‐‐the guy
I was talking about.
‐ They're with a woman, huh?
Let's hold off for now.
Just watch them.
‐ Right.
[indistinct murmuring]
GIRL: Can't be this cute...
[laughter]
[mysterious music]
♪ ♪
‐ I can handle the rest.
You go ahead and join
the others.
‐ But boss‐‐
‐ Just go already.
‐ Later.
♪ ♪
‐ What?
A girls' school smack
in the middle of Ikebukuro?
[girls giggling]
Oh, right, it's Sunday.
But the anticipation's
killing me.
‐ You got some business
with us or something?
[laughter]
MIKADO: Why would you do that?
Attacking people from Saitama?
That's crazy.
‐ They didn't give me
any choice.
After all, they were the ones
who spoiled the Ikebukuro tour
I was going to have
with you and Anri.
So it was payback.
Or is that not a good reason?
[laughter]
MIKADO: This is insane.
The Blue Squares...
a gang Masaomi feuded with.
I've heard of the Blue Squares.
If I remember it right,
they were a color gang
from around this area.
And they had a feud
with the Yellow Scarves.
‐ Well, you know
a lot more about us
than I would've thought.
I'm impressed, Mikado.
MIKADO: But Masaomi didn't
tell me everything.
‐ Ah, you noticed
I was tailing you.
‐ That's right, though you did
throw me off a little
when you stepped in front
of this girls' school.
You almost made me think that
my intuition was out of whack.
‐ You're a Dollar,
unless I'm mistaken.
‐ Well, I wouldn't argue
with you about that.
‐ I heard Shizuo Heiwajima's
also a Dollar.
Is that true?
‐ I guess you could say
that's true,
more or less.
That guy's got almost no clue
of how to be a team player.
‐ Yeah, he does seem
like that type.
[neck cracks]
‐ Well, you got a name,
or what?
[cell phone beeps]
Hmm?
CHIKAGE: You can answer that.
I'll wait for you.
[chuckles]
‐ It's an email.
[phones chiming and beeping]
‐ They really are all Dollars.
[electric guitar riff]
[gasps]
AOBA: Looks like
it's started, huh?
[laughter]
‐ What are you talking about?
What's started?
‐ Toramaru's inevitable revenge.
‐ What's wrong?
‐ You bastard.
What the hell are
you guys up to?
‐ I'm Chikage Rokujo,
by the way.
And, hey, I only
came to this town
to get some payback for the
fight that you guys started.
You can keep the change, though,
as long as you take this
in full.
[chuckles]
[leaves rustling]
MIKADO: You're the cause
of all this.
Why would you do something
like this?
And why did you admit it to me,
out of all people?
AOBA: Because I trust you,
Mikado.
‐ That's no answer at all, Aoba.
What do you plan to do with me?
‐ That's a good question.
It would've been better
if we'd done this
after you had a chance to get
to know us a little more.
But at this point,
we might as well
come right out and ask you.
Be our leader.
[laughter]
‐ What?
‐ I'm not asking you
to become the leader
of the Dollars.
No, that would break
the founding principle
of the Dollars.
[laughter]
So the thing I'm after here,
if you're willing,
is that I'd basically
like you to become
the leader of the Blue Squares.
‐ [gasps]
‐ Generally speaking,
we'll do as you say.
‐ Why? Why me?
AOBA: There are a lot of
reasons, to tell you the truth.
But I guess it's because
you hold a special position
in the Dollars.
‐ Special position?
AOBA:
To make a long story short,
it's because you're the one
who founded the Dollars.
‐ Uh...?
[laughter]
‐ Are you surprised that I know?
It just shows that we've got
a pretty decent
information‐gathering
network of our own.
[rock music]
‐ Damn that bastard.
I told him to never come back
to Ikebukuro.
And he set up shop
out here in the open!
[doorbell dings]
[grunting impatiently]
[growling]
Argh!
[latch clicks]
Huh?
WOMAN: Oh, really?
I guess it could be.
In your case, it's like,
at home you walk around
in the most indecorous manner.
‐ Indecorous? [laughing]
That sounds scandalous.
‐ [snarling]
MAN: It's not as bad
as all that.
Let's just say that I prefer
to unwind in my birthday suit
and leave it at that.
WOMAN: It's like you're
practically a nudist.
‐ Who the hell are you?
What's the big idea,
barging in?
Kid?
Bastard!
[tense bass music]
Shizuo!
Heiwajima was here.
I just saw him!
Get word out to Mr. Shiki
right now!
Shizuo wasted three of our guys!
[television droning]
AOBA: You'll be free to use us
in whatever way you want.
If that happens to be
stopping this gang war,
then just go ahead
and give the order.
If you tell us to crawl on
our knees to the Toramaru
and take a beating,
we'll accept that order.
Then again, if you tell us
to crush them instead,
then we'll go ahead
and do just that,
no matter what it might take.
‐ Doing that‐‐either of those‐‐
it's impossible!
There's no way I could do that!
What in the world made you think
I could ever
take on something like that,
when I want to avoid conflict?
All I have to do is
keep my mouth shut
about being a Dollar.
That's the kind of person I am.
If you're looking for a leader,
I'm definitely not your guy.
‐ That isn't true at all,
Mikado.
‐ [exhales sharply]
‐ And the thing that proves it
is the fact that right now...
you're smiling.
[laughter]
[slow dramatic music]
♪ ♪
‐ She said she wanted to come,
so I brought her along.
I wonder if I should have.
Don't worry, Akane.
The people who are supposed
to be meeting us here
are very nice.
‐ [whimpers]
♪ ♪
‐ Hey.
‐ Uh?
‐ Is something the matter?
‐ Ah, I just found out that all
the chat logs got deleted.
Maybe there was another storm.
‐ Or maybe everybody
just disappeared.
‐ Don't go all spooky on me.
[sighs]
♪ ♪
‐ [chuckles]
MASAOMI: He just ran and ran,
further inside the emptiness
of himself,
wondering if he really
did lose everything.
[eerie music]
‐ [chuckling]
[laughter continues]
♪ ♪
["Never Say Never" by
Three Lights Down Kings]
[man singing in Japanese]
♪ ♪
AKABAYASHI: Everywhere you go,
it's shady.
Everybody's sketchy.
It's always been
that kind of city.
But lately, it's getting worse.
Next time: "The Day Is Short,
The Work Is Long."
An ominous smell fills the air.