MIKADO: I still don't get it,
but I guess I sort of do.
Something
that seemed life‐changing,
but nothing changed at all.
It was really weird,
but the kind of weird
that could happen to anyone.
Half a year's gone by
since then.
[Cóiste‐Bodhar neighs]
[police siren wailing]
["Headhunt" by Okamoto's]
[man singing in Japanese]
♪ ♪
MIKADO: A world that I'd only
seen in manga and online
is right here in front of me.
‐ You're so lucky!
Don't just stand there.
Come on!
You want to see an urban legend?
‐ Don't jack with the cops,
monster.
‐ Huh? Whoa. What's with
the drastic outfit change?
‐ Masaomi, wake up!
‐ Masaomi!
‐ She and I
have this mutual friend,
and this guy who...
♪ ♪
‐ Carmilla Saizou is definitely
a force to be reckoned with.
The role is‐‐
‐ We interrupt
this scheduled programming
to bring you a breaking story.
MAN:
The police are currently engaged
in a high‐speed chase
with what appears to be
the Headless Rider!
‐ Not good.
Not good. Not good.
Not good. Not good!
‐ [chuckles]
[Cóiste‐Bodhar neighs]
‐ Oh!
‐ Ha! Don't think so.
Central,
this is Ikebukuro Three.
Send backup to my location.
IZAYA:
Huh. Never would've thought
something like that
would happen.
MAN: Unbelievable!
‐ So that's Kinnosuke Kuzuhara,
the motorcycle cop
I've been hearing about.
Can't tell
if this is good timing or bad.
[classical music]
‐ The rider in black,
at least for now,
is remaining silent
up on that rooftop.
[gasps]
Look at that!
It's a huge black object!
‐ Think you're Lupin the Third?
‐ Stay with us
as we continue our coverage
of that mysterious entity!
‐ Hmm.
‐ We'll bring you more exciting
details right after this‐‐
‐ [gasps]
It totally is mysterious!
How'd that bike
turn into a horse?
How'd it do that? How?
I mean, it's not CGI, right?
‐ Not so loud.
‐ Oh, I'm sorry.
But this stupid news
cutting into Yuhei's special
pisses me off.
I just can't contain myself!
Let's go.
I want to see.
It's all happening
right around here,
so come on‐‐
I can't take it anymore.
I want to go see!
‐ Calm down.
‐ I want to go see!
‐ Ah! I'm sorry!
I'm sorry, Ruri!
I'll calm down!
I'll calm down, okay?
[coughing]
No more habanero spray, please.
Think about it.
We're so lucky
to be living in an exciting city
with all this going on.
How thrilling is that, you know?
It's super thrilling, right?
Super magical.
So super badass!
[grunting]
‐ It's so exciting.
[police siren wailing]
‐ A mysterious object
is circling above‐‐
MAX: Whoa!
What's its deal?
What the heck
am I even looking at here?
It's something
mind‐blowingly awesome.
Something
out‐of‐this‐world powerful!
Oh, it makes me want to rush
over to Ikebukuro this second!
Hey! What's Mr. Yuhei up to?
He knows Ikebukuro,
so let's have him
show us around.
We'll go check out this rematch
of the legend of Sleepy Hollow
and then party
under the cherry blossoms!
‐ Mr. Sandshelt,
you're blocking the screen.
Please move.
‐ Oh. Uh, my bad.
Hey, hold on!
Where do you get off treating me
like I'm some
flame in the ass?
Is it 'cause
you can't work for a foreigner?
Come on, now.
Aren't the Japanese supposed to
be kind and respectful
towards their superiors?
Damn it!
My only allies are those who
raise themselves to an art form.
Every one of my adorable idols!
Only my angels
who spread happiness
over the world understand me,
and they always will, forever.
‐ Try to concentrate
on your job as president, sir.
‐ Hmm?
‐ We already went for a party in
the cherry blossoms last week,
and Yuhei Hanejima isn't
available now
because he's back at his home.
And, uh, why is it that
an American like yourself
has no grasp
of the English language?
‐ Ah!
I swear.
What a dull bunch you are.
What I want is something new
with impact
to get us out of
this rut we're in.
That's why I want to see
that mysterious headless rider.
Hold on.
I've got an idea!
Hiya. This is Sandshelt
of Jack O'Lantern calling.
Uh, it's Max.
[piano music]
‐ Half a year later.
The city hasn't changed at all.
He hasn't.
Or them.
Or her.
Or him.
And...
neither have we.
Sorry to take up your time,
Anri.
I realize
it's kind of a weird request.
‐ It's all right, Mikado.
I don't mind,
though I'm afraid
I haven't been very helpful
so far.
‐ I was a little surprised
a first‐year student
would ask me
to show them around Ikebukuro.
‐ Even though we commute here
every day,
we're surprisingly unfamiliar
with this area.
Like what kind of shops are
around,
or where someone can go
to find a good place to eat.
‐ We only know Russia's sushi.
‐ Yeah, I know.
‐ if only Masaomi were here.
‐ I wonder how he's doing.
‐ He's doing fine.
I'm sure of it.
‐ I hope so.
‐ He is.
Hey, Namie.
‐ What?
‐ Want to go get something
to eat?
‐ Huh?
‐ It's so boring around here.
I want to do something,
get out, and see some things.
Take in some culture.
It's pretty obvious
all kinds of things
are about to go down out there,
but it doesn't seem to have
much to do with me.
‐ If you and I went out to eat,
what would we even talk about?
‐ Things like the latest news
on your kid brother.
‐ Why?
Did something happen to Seiji?
IZAYA: Not really.
He's been with Mika Harima,
as usual.
It looks like
they're even deeper in love.
‐ I see.
As far as I'm concerned,
that's worthless information.
‐ [yawning]
It's the truth, though.
Maybe some news will come on
that will entertain me for once.
[exciting music]
‐ News 666.
In our top story this evening...
‐ We'll be covering
the serial murders
that have rocked
Ikebukuro recently.
The perpetrator has
yet to be caught.
‐ The incident occurred
this morning before dawn.
Employees rushed
into a second‐floor room
after hearing a scream
and witnessed a gruesome scene.
What they saw
was an unconscious woman,
drenched head to toe in blood,
and a dead man,
whose body was battered
beyond recognition,
lying in front of her.
This is the third murder
to take place in this manner.
But there's been no evidence
as of yet
to point to a plausible suspect.
Someone in a wolf mask
was spotted
at the first crime scene.
At the second,
witnesses reported seeing
a merman‐like figure
fleeing the site.
And today,
they were in a dinosaur mask
for this bizarre crime.
‐ I heard this scream,
so I ran out into the hall
to see what was going on.
And‐‐and the door was open,
so I could see inside,
but when I looked in, um,
this dinosaur thing‐‐
well, he looked like a monster,
you know?
Going at that guy's chest
with his bare hands.
[both groaning]
I could see him gouging‐‐
‐ The titles due for release
this month are awesome.
‐ Huh?
‐ The irregular
magic high school.
‐ So no new volume
of a certain magical index?
‐ Dotachin,
you're into light novels?
‐ Nope, those things are totally
beyond my understanding.
But that one's a pretty
interesting read.
‐ Sorry, man. Afraid there isn't
a new release out this month.
‐ If they stick
to their usual schedule,
it should come out
in a couple of months.
‐ Gotcha.
Give me a heads‐up
when it does, okay?
‐ Hollywood's at it again?
‐ Huh?
Who's Hollywood?
‐ It's that murderer's nickname.
It's all over the Internet, man.
That's what everyone started
calling him online.
‐ Why do they call him
"Hollywood"?
‐ Probably because he uses all
those badass costumes
and makeup.
‐ It's so Hollywood!
Like that, huh?
‐ Mm‐hmm.
‐ I don't know his deal.
The way he kills isn't normal.
‐ It's beyond normal.
I hear it's actually way more
brutal than the reports say.
Apparently, all the media
were told to tone stuff down.
‐ Breaks down walls and doors
with his bare hands,
and then they say he strips
every shred of flesh
off his victims
so there's nothing left
but the bone.
‐ He takes people out
like he's some animal,
but he's human on the outside.
The guy kind of sounds like
he's Death Gun from "SAO"
or something.
‐ I'm thinking
he's actually more like
Gastrea from "Black Bullet."
‐ I'm thinking he's actually
more like
Yuuki Katakura from
"Double Brid."
‐ And I'm thinking to myself,
"Why are you guys enjoying this
so much?"
‐ Well, it's time for us to be
heading out.
‐ We'll be seeing you two later.
‐ Where are you guys off to?
‐ We're heading out to see
Mikabu.
‐ Said he wants to ask us
something,
but it's very hush‐hush.
‐ We'd like to take this time
to ask for your help.
[exciting music]
♪ ♪
We'll be calling on you,
our viewers,
for any information you might
have.
‐ You've gotten to be
quite the celebrity, Celty.
‐ Guess I'll just go on TV,
then.
‐ What? Seriously?
MAN:
Well, as a matter of fact...
‐ I'm kidding.
I'm gonna go do that job now.
‐ Okay.
If anything happens,
get out quick.
CELTY: Don't worry.
I'll be right back.
‐ Celty!
I'd be devastated
if something happened!
Please! No!
I don't know what I'd do
without you.
‐ Enough. I get it, all right?
SHINRA: Celty?
Rub rub.
Ah!
‐ And now something special.
‐ An interview with someone
who's a big hit
with women these days.
MAN: Yuhei Hanajima.
Date of birth unknown.
Estimated age‐‐
21.
He debuted in
"Vampire Ninja: Carmilla Saizo."
His good looks
and knockout performance
ignited his popularity.
Appearing nonstop
in high‐profile TV shows
and films,
his versatility gained him
critical acclaim, even overseas.
‐ [vocalizing]
MAN: Not content being
just an actor,
he also crossed into
variety shows.
On the show "How Much Can You
Increase
the Worth of a Million
Yen in a Month,"
he used his wits to increase
his capital to 1.2 billion yen.
On a hidden camera show,
he was surrounded by Yakuza
and pressured to cut off
his pinky.
As he was about to chop it off,
the crew rushed in
and stopped him just in time.
‐ When it comes
to whatever Yuhei's thinking,
I honestly draw a total blank,
since the guy's usually
as silent as a Buddha.
Even to me, he's all
"no, thanks" when we talk.
Like this poster?
It was my idea,
but I heard some talk that
Yuhei didn't really like it.
No reaction whatsoever.
Like a cold fish.
I got fed up, went to America,
and he was all "no problem"
and stuff.
I swear, what a prima donna.
Aren't I?
MAN: And we've managed to get
an exclusive interview
with this man.
We'll see
the real Yuhei Hanejima.
WOMAN: In your personal life,
you're known
for being somewhat poker‐faced.
How did this come about?
‐ It's because my older brother
had violent mood swings,
so I tried not to be like him
while growing up.
Still, I do have a lot
of respect for him despite that.
‐ Hmph.
WOMAN: I see. All right.
‐ Shizuo.
‐ Huh?
‐ Let's get going.
‐ Right.
‐ "Carmilla Saizou:
The Beginning."
‐ Carmilla Saizou is definitely
a force to be reckoned with.
EMILIA: All right.
That should do it.
I'm completely finished.
I want to thank you
for allowing us
to perform
this illicit research.
‐ Emilia,
it's not illicit research.
It's scientific research.
‐ Oh, my!
I'm sorry about that,
but I sincerely wish
you would call me Mother.
If you did,
I would most certainly rain down
a torrent of appreciation
in return for that.
Or maybe Mommy.
Mamma Mia.
‐ What's wrong?
‐ Nothing.
It's just that, normally,
you'd be jabbing me in the ribs
by now
or yanking my cheek out
like this.
‐ Actually, I am seducing you.
‐ [sighs]
[doorbell rings]
What the?
Aw, just when
it was getting good.
Coming.
‐ Hi!
A full‐grown Japanese male.
It's really you, isn't it,
Dr. Shinra Kishitani?
‐ Huh? Hey!
Hold on!
EMILIA: [laughing and squealing]
SHINRA: [muffled groaning]
‐ Ah! Look at you!
Celty!
‐ Hey! Wait!
EMILIA: I've been waiting
for this moment for so long!
‐ Who are you?
‐ Oh.
How rude of me.
My name is Emilia, of course.
I happen to be your father,
Shingen's, second wife.
So exciting.
We got married in America.
BOTH: What?
SHINGEN: Call her "Mother."
‐ What? Dad?
When'd you get here?
‐ Well, the thing is...
While I can't deny I've been
thinking about my future
where Shinra's concerned...
it's nothing concrete
like marriage yet.
‐ You're basically living
like a common law couple.
‐ Ah!
Don't sneak up like that!
SHINGEN: Well, you did agree to
be an experimental subject
on the condition that
a female researcher
would be the point of contact.
That's why I'm using this‐‐
‐ That's not the problem!
SHINGEN: You've already
married into my family,
more or less, Celty.
I want you to treat Emilia
like a mother.
‐ Mm‐hmm, mm‐hmm!
‐ Thanks a lot.
‐ I must admit that never in my
wildest dreams
did I think I'd be accepting
a Dullahan as Shinra's bride.
A headless rider.
A headless bride.
A headless klutz.
Interacting with you is like
one eye‐opener after another.
‐ Don't you have any second
thoughts about taking advantage
of your son's bride for
your research?
‐ It truly pains me to do so,
but it can't be helped.
I'm afraid I can't afford to
turn down a request
that's straight
from Nebula headquarters.
‐ So we'll be cutting away
at you a lot.
‐ Whatever.
Could you just pay me
for this job?
SHINGEN: Emilia,
please give her the money.
‐ You only need to give
the word,
and it shall be done, dear.
Payment as promised.
[cash register clinks]
‐ Received. Thank you.
[Cóiste‐Bodhar neighs]
Wow, it's hard to believe
I made a million yen
in just one week.
[gasps]
I'm gonna use this
to buy Shinra some new glasses.
And then‐‐
I know.
Why don't I treat him
to something really good to eat?
[laughs]
He's always said he wanted
to eat pickled yellowtail,
hasn't he?
Wait. Is yellowtail
even in season now?
‐ Excuse me.
I'm sorry to bother you,
but do you have a minute?
I'm Fukumi with Dio TV,
and I'd like to ask you
a question or two,
if you wouldn't mind.
‐ Crap. Don't tell me.
‐ I'm currently reporting
on traffic etiquette
here in the city.
And your motorcyle‐‐
it doesn't seem to have
lights or a license plate.
Were you aware those are
violations of the law?
Would it be safe to assume
that you are the black rider?
[Cóiste‐Bodhar neighs]
Uh?
I'd appreciate a comment.
How do you justify this?
Riding around
on a dangerous bike?
‐ What should I do?
I can't say, "I'm a monster,
so please overlook it."
Huh? Maybe I could.
If I show him something
unbelievable,
it might get edited out,
and it might look like CG
if it's aired.
‐ Hmm?
What's this?
"This is a horse, so it has
no headlights or license plate."
Come on.
Are you joking?
‐ Is everything clear now?
If so, I'll be on my way.
‐ [whimpering]
KINNOSUKE: Hey.
Where do you think you're going?
Riding without lights
is a punishable offense,
even on motorless modes
of transportation.
Monster.
‐ Uh?
[neighing]
‐ Call the studio!
[police siren wailing]
[Cóiste‐Bodhar neighs]
♪ ♪
‐ Not good.
Not good. Not good.
Not good. Not good!
‐ It's a huge black object!
[cell phone ringing]
‐ Oh, you finally picked up.
So, Celty, looks like
you've got yourself into
some trouble there.
But that was
a pretty slick trick.
Using your shadows to make
copies of yourself,
your bike, and that glider,
and then launching them off
the roof to use as a decoy.
Anyway, I think starting today,
things are gonna get pretty busy
for a while,
so there's something
we need to be clear about.
Until the chaos settles down,
stay away from my workplace.
I'll email you the details, but
I called so that you don't
come by before you
get a chance to read it.
Later!
Best of luck.
MAN: The mysterious object is
circling above Ikebukuro
Station.
Its destination‐‐
‐ What's with him?
No, it's gone!
It's gone!
I dropped it somewhere!
I must've dropped it!
[engines approaching]
‐ Hey! It's the Black Rider!
‐ Huh?
‐ Let's get our 10 million yen!
MAN: Whoo‐hoo!
[men shouting excitedly]
‐ Did you see that reward
on the net?
‐ Yeah! A cool 10 mil!
‐ Think it's Celty?
‐ Let's go see.
MAN: You little brats
disrespecting the Dollars?
‐ No, we're not.
‐ You bastards.
You're a bunch
of damn petty thieves!
[both panting]
‐ Like I said, you're so lucky.
Don't just stand there.
Come on.
You want to see an urban legend?
MIKADO: It's true.
We haven't changed.
‐ The black bike!
The headless rider!
♪ ♪
MIKADO: Compared to back then,
a lot of things have changed.
[dreamy music]
♪ ♪
[Cóiste‐Bodhar neighs]
[riders cheering]
[all laughing]
MIKADO: But nothing about us
has changed.
‐ Huh? Not watching?
‐ Nah.
[yawns]
MIKADO: Or should have.
[man singing in Japanese]
♪ ♪
MAN: Ikebukuro.
The city that never sleeps.
Night and day, people come and
go, meeting and parting.
Suspicious murderer.
Suspicious new students.
Suspicious Russians.
Next time, "Harmony Is
the Greatest of Virtues."