["Day You Laugh"
by Toyonaga Toshiyuki]
[mellow rock music]
♪ ♪
[man singing
in Japanese]
♪ ♪
‐ [panting]
‐ Oof! Ah!
[electricity crackling]
MAN: She has knowledge,
but mentally she's a child.
‐ Before I say anything,
promise you won't tell
my mom and dad
what we talk about.
VARONA: He's not like
the Black Bike
or that girl with the glasses.
And he doesn't have that oddness
about him like those others.
No doubt about it,
this man is human.
[man singing in Japanese]
♪ ♪
BOY: Dude, you hear about
Shizuo Heiwajima?
BOY: What about him?
GIRL: He had some little
chick with him.
BOY: Picked a fight
with the Mob.
GIRL: He climbed the side
of a building.
BOY: My buddy saw him
jump out of a car
with a little girl
in his arms!
This biker babe stabbed him.
GIRL: Hey, did you hear?
BOY: You know that Shizuo guy?
BOY: Dude, I heard he's dead.
BOY: Stabbed by some bitch.
GIRL: Hit by a semi.
BOY: He pissed off the Mob,
and they threw him
off a building.
BOY: Check it out, man.
I heard Shizuo
got hit by a truck,
and now he's on life support.
BOY: Yakuza was chasing him.
He jumped off a building,
and, bam, pancake!
BOY: He's in the hospital
all effed up.
BOY: Nah, I saw him
walking around.
MAN: Who's freaking out?
Now's our chance
to bury him for good.
MAN: Dude, you haven't even
heard the best part.
He's got a girlfriend now,
and get this‐‐
chick's got a frickin' kid!
BOY: A kid?!
You got to be shittin' me!
‐ No way.
You're that
Shizuo Heiwajima guy.
BOTH: Hmm?
‐ So you're Yuhei Hanejima's
brother.
‐ Son of a‐‐
‐ If news got out that
a thug like you is family,
his career would go
right down the toilet.
MAN: Now's the time, man.
MAN: It's perfect.
‐ [sighs]
‐ So how about you
forget what I owe,
I keep my mouth shut,
and we call it square?
Sound good?
‐ [growling]
[fist smacking]
‐ Aaaahhhhh!
MAN: You and me,
we can take out Shizuo.
‐ [panting]
VARONA: Why?
Why have I agreed
to subject myself to this?
‐ Remember, we're in
the service industry.
Try to look more,
I don't know, friendly.
‐ I refute your insinuation.
I do not have unfriendly look.
It is as always is.
‐ Ah, Varona, Varona.
This no good.
You must not frown like that.
The customer is god, yes?
He patient, but he's only
going so far.
You may insult Buddha
up to three time.
But with god, you can go
high as hundred.
‐ What does that mean?
Your language is beyond
my comprehension.
MAN: Look who's talking.
‐ Why do I subject myself
to this hell?
‐ [speaking Russian]
[struggling noises]
‐ [speaks Russian]
‐ [in English] I was thinking
of doing that.
It's now shame
of losing stronger.
[speaking Russian]
‐ [speaking Russian]
‐ [in English] I wanted
to destroy everything‐‐
myself most of all.
‐ [in English] Varona, they say
those not work, not happy.
But if smile,
sushi come to you.
‐ [in English] Good point.
Maybe work is what's needed.
SIMON: Ugh!
Now we sued for sex harassment!
Sex harassment no good!
Hara‐kiri for all
sex harassers!
‐ I swear to God, Seiji, you
better not be eyeballing her.
‐ All I wanted to know
was limit of human strength.
But reading books
could not help me find answer.
So I decided to go
and find it for myself.
But when I came here,
I learned hard truth:
that I am weak.
Black Bike is monster,
so it does not count,
but bartender different.
It was strange sensation.
[eerie music]
Is hard to explain.
It was like every cell in brain
wanted to fighting.
But at same time,
muscles wanted to run away.
My whole body was shaking.
At last, after
so many encounters
with all kinds of people,
he was the one‐‐
the challenge I was looking for.
But I am weak.
I do not have strength enough
to test limits of his.
Perhaps everything I have done‐‐
[man speaking on phone]
The training, the missions‐‐
are meaningless.
SEIJI: I think that ringtone
is kinda creepy.
‐ Are you kidding? I love it.
[phone buzzing]
VARONA: So what left?
What is point
of living anymore?
MIZUKI: We're just here
to say hey and scope it out.
You don't like it,
say the word, and we're gone.
‐ What do I have to do to get
strong enough to kill someone?
‐ You got someone
you really hate that bad?
‐ Uh‐uh.
It's just something
I have to do.
He's a good man,
but I still have to kill him.
‐ 'Cause you want him dead?
‐ Mm‐mm.
Not really, no.
‐ Well, then why
do you want to?
‐ 'Cause if I don't,
they said he's gonna kill
everyone I love!
‐ Who'd go and tell you that?
‐ Um...
‐ All right, so this guy
you got to off,
he, like, a good person?
‐ I don't know.
I'm not sure.
I don't know anything.
Everyone's been lying to me‐‐
my friends, their moms,
my own dad.
I don't even know if I can
really trust you, either.
I'm pretty sure
he's not a bad man,
but it's just a feeling.
But then I think,
"How can I trust me?"
I‐‐I just‐‐
I don't know.
All I know is
I have to get stronger...
somehow.
‐ [chuckles]
Well, little lady,
I'm shocked.
I didn't know all you kids
these days walked around town
thinking stuff like that.
[chuckles]
Well, if he turns out
to be a bad guy, get ready.
You'll have
to shut him down quick.
And that means you got to be
stronger than him,
or you're toast.
That said, there's other ways
of dealing with stuff like this
besides killing.
‐ How?
‐ Toughen yourself up so you
can protect you and your family.
Better for everyone in the end.
MAIRU: No way!
We got the Awakusu
in the house!
‐ [gasps]
‐ What the heck are you doing
with that cute little girl?
Did you kidnap her
or something?
‐ Come on, Miss Mairu.
You know better than that.
Do I look like some kind
of evil creep to you?
MAIRU: You do have that
"hey, I'm a sketchy guy"
vibe going on.
MIZUKI: That's harsh.
Listen up, guys, this
young lady's name is Akane.
She's the granddaughter
of my company's boss.
‐ [gasps] No, no!
Don't tell them that!
‐ Yeah? That's so cool!
It's an honor to meet the next
in line of the Awakusus.
‐ [whimpering]
‐ [laughs] What the heck are
you doing back there, kid?
‐ She's just trying
to beat you up.
Here's a tip: you got to hit him
where it counts.
Huh!
‐ [grunts]
Jeez.
How about you leave her training
to the professionals?
‐ Is that why she's here?
To join our dojo?
‐ Maybe.
She wants to check it out first.
‐ If you go, I will let you
be my sidekick.
And if you do
everything I say,
I'll teach you
my ultimate technique:
the Thumbtack Special.
‐ Seriously?
Sounds like the dorkiest
fighting move ever.
MAIRU: Oh, stuff it, old man.
‐ Uhh!
‐ Come on.
‐ [whimpering]
‐ [giggles]
‐ Just call your pops
when you're finished,
and somebody'll swing by
and get you, okay?
‐ O‐okay.
‐ [chuckles]
TOM: You're famous;
your brother's famous.
That's the price you pay
for celebrity.
SHIZUO: I guess.
‐ [gasps]
‐ I guarantee that won't be
the last time that happens.
‐ It still sucks.
SIMON: Shizuo and Mr. Tom!
Welcome!
TOM: Hey, you ever thank
that geeky doc
for getting you out
of that jam yesterday?
‐ No, not yet.
TOM: Even though you guys
are tight,
he stepped up for you.
He deserves a call, at least.
‐ I know.
You're right.
I'll call him now.
‐ Blonde...
sunglasses...
dress like bartender.
It is him!
SHIZUO: Hey, Shinra.
Look, sorry for the trouble
yesterday.
Just calling to say thanks
and, uh...
Huh? Yeah, sure.
I'll try and catch you
later then.
‐ What's up?
‐ He said to call back.
Guess he must be busy.
The weird thing is,
he sounded all choked up.
‐ What's his problem?
Ah!
Don't look now, but that girl's
totally giving us the eye.
‐ Hmm?
Oh, the blonde?
Must be new.
Or maybe they never had her
out front before.
‐ Yo, Dennis.
How long has that gorgeous
girl over there
been working here?
She Russian too?
‐ Yeah, she's Russian.
But we're still training her,
so she's about as useless
as a matryoshka doll.
‐ Huh.
And if I want to tell her
she's foxy in Russian,
what do I have to say?
‐ [speaking Russian]
‐ "Bee, archera bartend nen."
Thanks. Hey!
"Bee, archera bartend nen!"
‐ Mm?
‐ Eh, heh?
‐ [speaking Russian]
‐ [speaks Russian]
‐ Did I screw up
the pronunciation
that bad or something?
‐ Sorry, you're asking
the wrong guy.
‐ Talk about putting
my foot in my mouth.
Oh, crap, she looks like
I pissed her off.
‐ I bet it's 'cause
of your lame pickup line.
‐ Really?
Oh, man.
‐ So, gents, how's business
these days?
‐ Huh?
DENNIS: You know, you slammed?
You need an extra hand
or anything?
‐ Oh.
Yeah, we got deadbeats
coming out of the woodwork‐‐
more than me and Shizuo
can handle,
you want to know the truth.
‐ Really?
You're in luck.
You need someone, you're welcome
to put her to work.
BOTH: Hmm?
[quirky musical flourish]
‐ Mm.
[laid‐back music]
♪ ♪
‐ I can't believe the boss
is cool with this.
Uh...
‐ I also have concern.
I have not been told what
this job requires me to do.
‐ She should be pushing papers
at a desk
instead of out here
hustling with us.
Listen up.
We're in collections,
so our job's to get money
from scumbags who don't pay up.
You got it?
‐ We are to collect
protection money.
I understand.
‐ Actually, it ain't exactly
protection money.
She ain't gonna work, man.
No way.
[quirky instrumental music]
‐ Mm.
♪ ♪
MAN: I don't got any idea
what you're talking' about.
‐ Hey, if you want me
to spell it out,
that's cool.
See, you owe our boss some‐‐
‐ Need a hand here!
[indistinct chatter]
Now, what was it
you were trying to sell me?
'Cause we're in the market
for some blowjobs
from that fine lady.
[laughter]
‐ I knew this was gonna happen.
‐ Hey, what up, baby?
TOM: Hmm?
SHIZUO: Huh?
‐ Ugh!
‐ [gasps]
MAN: What the‐‐no, wait‐‐ugh!
[pummeling]
‐ You bitch!
Ugh!
‐ Argh!
[upbeat instrumental music]
MAN: Did you see that?
MAN: Yeah, who was the chick
with Shizuo?
MAN: I thought he was
all busted up.
MAN: He really does have
a girlfriend, yo.
MAN: Nah, she's with that
homie with the dreads.
MAN: Nah, you trippin'.
I seen 'em all together,
and she was scopin' Shizuo hard.
♪ ♪
‐ Should've known you'd have
some tricks up your sleeve.
After all, you're friends
with Simon and Dennis.
‐ So, uh, you into
martial arts or something?
'Cause you're
pretty damn strong.
‐ I have studied basic of many
different kind of discipline.
Dennis and Samya,
or rather Simon,
as you call him‐‐
I learn everything
I know from them.
‐ Hmm, well, whatever your
deal is, you're a badass.
‐ Comment seems facetious coming
from someone with your skill.
‐ Hmm?
You know about Shizuo's rep?
‐ One cannot help but hear rumor
on streets of Ikebukuro.
TOM: Ain't that the truth.
‐ Now I am closer
to Shizuo Heiwajima...
and closer to discovering
limits of human strength.
However...
SHIZUO: I don't know what kind
of rumors you've been hearing.
But I guarantee
I got nothing on you.
‐ I am afraid
I do not understand.
‐ I didn't train to be this way;
I just am.
It's like being strong
ain't the same
as having real strength.
I think people like you who work
hard and train to be stronger,
they're the ones
who deserve the props.
That takes determination.
‐ That reminds me,
who's that one martial artist
guy you were into?
You know, the weird name guy?
‐ Yeah,
Traugott Geissendorfer.
Man, that guy's something else.
‐ Well, if you ask me,
I think you kick way more ass
than he does.
Hell, if you wanted to,
I bet you could win yourself
a gold medal
in weightlifting easy.
Wait...are gold medals
even made out of gold?
VARONA: Gold medals in
Olympic Games contain real gold,
but they are not solid gold.
It will be too expensive
for economically challenged
host country.
Medals are 92.5% pure silver.
Then it is plated
with 6 grams of gold.
Solid gold was used for
Nobel Prize medals until 1980.
Since then, medals are only
75% gold with pure gold plating.
‐ Why'd they do that
to the Nobel Prize?
‐ Pure gold
extremely soft element.
If you bite,
it will leave mark.
Using alloy instead
prevents damage.
‐ Wow.
‐ You're hot, a badass,
and friggin' smart.
Triple threat, yo.
‐ I disagree.
I am neither pretty nor smart,
nor am I strong.
AKANE: Hey, Shizuo!
‐ Here comes trouble.
‐ Shizuo!
SHIZUO: Hey, Akane.
‐ [giggles]
‐ What is that girl doing here?
MAN: Yo, dude, check it.
The rumors about him are true.
MAN: Holy crap, that kid
just hugged him.
MAN: That's Shizuo's kid?
MAN: That's his baby
and his baby mama!
‐ If she's here,
so are Awakusu.
‐ Whoa!
‐ She's so pretty.
‐ Who's your friend?
Can I hug her?
Huh?
‐ Better not.
‐ Thanks so much for yesterday.
‐ [chuckles]
Yeah, sure, it was nothing.
You want to really thank me,
just keep right on smiling.
‐ So Shizuo and Akane
are friends?
‐ I know, right?
‐ So how did you guys
end up together?
‐ Akane just signed up
at Mairu's dojo today.
‐ Yeah? You're taking some
self‐defense classes, huh?
Smart move, kiddo.
Doesn't hurt to learn that.
‐ Wow, you think so?
I'll work really hard.
‐ Hey, you hear about
what happened?
It's all over the news.
SHIZUO: No, what's up?
‐ How does he not know
about it?
‐ I can correct that.
Izaya was‐‐
TOM: Whoops, sorry, ladies.
We got to get going.
‐ Yeah.
TOM: The next stop's got
a wife and kids.
Might be tricky.
You mind sitting this one out?
‐ I will stay here then.
AKANE: I'll wait
for you, Shizuo!
Hurry back!
[cell phone ringing]
MAN: Hey, it's me.
He just left the girls.
You ready?
MAN: Yeah, yeah, give me a sec,
will ya?
MAN: What are we gonna do
with them high school chicks?
MAN: Screw it, we'll take 'em
with us, too.
‐ Since you're Russian,
I bet you know Simon.
Do you know this other Russian
called Egor, too?
‐ Yes, I know him.
I am surprised a girl like you
would be aware of him, though.
Most unusual.
MAIRU: Wow, small world.
‐ Excuse me, but are you
Shizuo's friend,
or his girlfriend?
‐ I deny friendship with him
and girlfriendship.
We are coworkers,
and that is enough.
‐ Ah, oh, that's good.
[tires screeching]
‐ Hmm.
[indistinct muttering]
‐ Uh‐oh, this doesn't
look good, you guys.
[techno music]
‐ Kidnappers.
‐ [gasps]
‐ We'll take care
of Legs McBlonde here.
‐ You guys bag the rest
of the bitches.
‐ [sighs]
‐ Ugh!
‐ Holy shit!
‐ Uhh?
[screaming]
Ow!
‐ [giggles]
‐ Huh?
‐ Die!
‐ Argh!
[thump]
‐ [giggles]
‐ A stun gun?
‐ Shit, who are these chicks?
‐ We can't use them
as hostages against Shizuo.
We can't even touch 'em!
‐ Interesting.
These imbeciles are trying
to take down Heiwajima.
‐ [grunting and groaning]
‐ Very funny.
These fools against him?
Ridiculous.
They are more pathetic
than weakest opponents
I have ever faced.
They may try, but there
is not enough of them,
not nearly.
Humans are not so fragile.
Heiwajima is not so fragile.
And after so many defeats,
I almost forgot what I am,
what drives me, my nature.
I almost forgot
the pleasure I felt.
To test human strength
was only pleasure.
I liked and felt a pleasure
only when destroying others.
[gunshots]
Is different now.
Now I just want to be stronger.
He is target:
a man harder than diamond,
a man stronger than tundra.
I will destroy him!
‐ [grunting]
‐ Holy shit,
let's get out of here!
[panting]
[tires screeching]
Those assholes bailed on us!
‐ Look! Shizuo's back!
MAN: Run!
MAN: This ain't over!
‐ What the hell?
Did we miss a fight?
‐ Who goes and picks a fight
at a shrine?
Bunch of lowlife dickwads.
‐ I wish to change answer
to earlier question
about Shizuo Heiwajima.
‐ Huh?
‐ He is not coworker.
He is prey.
And one day, I swear
I will destroy him.
‐ No! You can't!
‐ Akane!
‐ Y‐you can't kill him!
I'm the one who's supposed to!
I saw Shizuo first, and‐‐
and I'm gonna kill him!
I mean, I don't really
want to kill him,
but still, I, um...
I don't know.
All I know is I have
to come up with a way
to get rid of him.
‐ You make no sense.
Please explain
this exclusive claim
you insist you have on my prey.
‐ How?
I don't know anything
about stuff like that!
‐ What's up?
‐ Nothing.
Where's Shizuo?
‐ Getting cigs, why?
‐ He is not!
You better not lay a finger
on Shizuo,
'cause he's mine!
‐ Whoa.
‐ Sorry, Tom, what'd I miss?
‐ Shizuo, you're back!
‐ Yeah, you guys get along?
[quirky music]
♪ ♪
‐ Hmm?
MAN: God damn it!
Who the hell were those chicks?
‐ Dude, they're Shizuo's women.
What'd you expect?
‐ Next time, we wait
till the kid's alone,
then we snatch her.
‐ There ain't gonna be
a next time, punk!
‐ Huh?
‐ Why don't you go f...
[indistinct muttering]
‐ [gasps]
‐ His brother's good‐looking,
so's he...
it's got to be in the genes.
‐ You've been acting weird.
What's going on, Tom?
‐ Huh?
Oh, nothing.
‐ Hmm.
Mind if I ask you something?
‐ What is it?
‐ Have we, like,
met somewhere before?
Hmm?
‐ What's up?
‐ I am sorry.
Is secret I wish to keep.
I hope you do not mind.
‐ Hmm.
[coins clinking]
‐ Take it.
My treat.
Look, over the years,
I've gone through a lot of jobs.
But I've never had
to train anyone before.
If you don't want to tell me,
that's cool.
Seeing as how you're here
'cause of Simon
and seeing as how
Akane seems to dig you,
you can't be all that bad.
Anyway, I'm looking forward
to working with you.
‐ Thank you.
‐ [chuckles]
‐ You are strange person,
Shizuo Heiwajima.
It appears I have much
to learn about you yet.
From now on, it will be
new reason for living.
I like forward to work
with you, as well.
MAN: The Awakusus took out those
thugs who were after Shizuo!
MAN: Yeah, that's 'cause
his chick's in the Awakusu.
MAN: That ain't it.
It's 'cause Shizuo's
the bastard son of the boss.
MAN: I think I'm done
going after him, man.
MAN: Not 'cause we're
scared of him or nothing.
MAN: No, we just don't want to
be on the Awakusu's shit list.
MAN: Yeah.
We ain't scared, though.
["Exit" by Revalcy]
[man singing in Japanese]
♪ ♪
ANRI: The city's in chaos again.
As rumors spread
about the Dollars,
there's a psychotic stalker
lurking in the background.
And like it or not,
we're about to get dragged
into the nightmare.
Next time, "Asleep or Awake."