["Day You Laugh"
by Toyonaga Toshiyuki]
♪ ♪
[man singing in Japanese]
NAMIE:
Seiji's in his second year.
I wish
I could've congratulated him.
MIKA: The moment I saw you,
I fell in love.
When our eyes met,
you smiled at me.
NAMIE: Pretty, huh?
MIKA: Come on, Seiji.
Show me your face again.
‐ Your big sis
will handle it all.
You want Seiji to love you,
right?
SEIJI: I do love you...
Celty.
♪ ♪
[cell phone vibrating]
[tone chirping]
‐ Must be on another call.
If Shizuo Heiwajima got framed,
the only one who'd benefit
would be Izaya Orihara.
If that's true,
I bet that prick's tight
with the Russians too.
[moody jazz music]
Oh well.
I'll leave him alone for now.
I better watch him, though.
Give a punk like that an inch,
and who knows what he'll do?
If he gets out of line,
I guess
I'll just have to bury his ass.
AOBA: Izaya Orihara,
I don't know if you knew,
but you and I
might be underestimating Mikado.
He might be way smarter
than we originally thought.
He's a mystery,
and that makes him dangerous.
You know that, right,
Izaya Orihara?
JINNAI: Oh, and since you asked,
my name is Jinnai Yodogiri,
and I'm pleased
to make your acquaintance.
CELTY:
I just thought of something.
Is Jinnai Yodogiri tied in
with the Awakusus?
‐ Who? Oh, you mean
the missing CEO
of that talent agency.
I guess he might be,
but I don't know if he is
for sure.
Why? What's up?
‐ Mr. Shiki asked me
to give him a heads‐up
if I ever spotted him in town.
‐ Really?
I wonder if it's got
anything to do with Ruri.
IZAYA: This is bad.
Got to... get...
a hold of Namie.
[ambulance siren wailing]
WOMAN: Here's our next story.
Around 9:00 last night,
in a shopping arcade
near Sendai Station,
a man was critically stabbed
by an unknown assailant.
The victim has been identified
as Izaya Orihara.
A large crowd had formed
by the time police arrived.
Several witnesses told us
that Mr. Orihara collapsed
in a heap in the street‐‐
‐ So he went and got himself
stabbed, huh?
This could be bad for him.
If any of the people
he's crossed hear the news,
they'll head over to Tohoku
to finish the job.
I guess he won't be coming back
here for a while,
so I'll have the place
all to myself.
WOMAN: Find out
if this was a random attack.
[Namie sighs]
‐ Seiji.
♪ ♪
[door whooshes]
‐ Huh?
Good morning, Seiji!
‐ Morning, Mika.
‐ Where do you want to go?
It doesn't matter
where you want,
as long as we're together.
‐ Okay.
Do you want to go see a movie?
MAIRU: The second
he put his hand on her shoulder,
Mika threw her arms around him
and kept walking along.
If it were me, I'd be all,
"I can't walk like this."
He sure didn't look like
he minded it, though.
KURURI: They were lovey‐dovey.
♪ ♪
‐ Is something wrong?
‐ No, it's nothing.
Go on.
What happened next?
‐ Oh. Well, after all that PDA,
they went
to the Metropolitan Theatre.
Right now, they're watching
"Vampire Ninja: Carmilla Saizou
Beginnings."
They're still‐‐
oh, wait.
No, I bet it's over by now.
‐ In ten minutes.
‐ Good.
Thank you both
for keeping tabs on them
up to now and reporting it.
Here's your fee, as promised.
300,000 yen.
Please destroy the card
after you withdraw the funds.
‐ Are you sure you're cool
with paying us that much?
‐ Well, of course.
Is there a problem
with the amount you're getting?
MAIRU: No, but all we did
was spy on your brother.
This is a lot of money.
‐ Don't be silly.
It's a bargain
as far as I'm concerned.
Knowing where Seiji goes
and what he does
is valuable to me,
and in case you're wondering,
that amount reflects
all the time
you spent on the job.
I took your hours
and multiplied it
by what Izaya pays me per hour.
I don't see
why you shouldn't get that too.
‐ I don't know
what she does for Izaya,
but she makes bank off him.
‐ Maybe he doesn't know
the day's salary.
‐ By the way,
did either of you hear
about what happened
to your brother today?
‐ Yeah. We know all about
how he got stabbed by someone.
‐ The police notified us
this morning.
‐ They couldn't get hold
of our folks
'cause they're overseas.
I guess
that's why they called us.
I told them to spit on the gash
and slap some tape on it.
They got mad, though.
They were all,
"How can you say things"‐‐
NAMIE:
Their brother got stabbed,
but they don't even seem
to be upset about it.
I guess he must not be
that important to them.
How bizarre.
Since you're here,
I was wondering
about something else.
MAIRU: Sure! What?
‐ The girl‐‐
how does Seiji address her
when he speaks to her?
‐ Huh?
‐ Hmm.
‐ Just by her first name‐‐
you know, Mika.
They've been going out
for a year now,
and everyone I ask said
he's been calling her that
this whole time,
so I guess that‐‐
[ceramic shatters]
Um...uh...
[patrons murmuring]
Uh, Ms. Namie?
‐ Are you feeling ill?
‐ That bitch.
‐ [gasps]
NAMIE: Not once has Seiji
ever called me by my first name.
Not once.
‐ How'd you like it?
‐ It was awesome.
And you know why?
'Cause I was next to you
the whole time.
[giggles]
‐ That's really sweet, but what
did you think about the movie?
Like, did all that time paradox
stuff make sense to you?
MIKA: Yeah, I think so.
I mean, the future didn't change
all that much, right?
So I figure that stuff in
the past wasn't the real past.
It was a parallel universe
with a different timeline.
What do you think?
SEIJI: Yeah. That's pretty much
what I thought too.
‐ See, we do think alike.
‐ All those monsters
and vampires
made me remember it again.
‐ What? You mean her head?
♪ ♪
SEIJI: Yeah.
My sister too.
The last time anyone saw her
was more than six months ago.
If anyone knows where
that head is, it's her.
‐ You should be worried
about your sister more.
‐ Why?
‐ 'Cause I bet
a whole lot of people
are after her right now.
She might even be in danger.
‐ She can take care of herself
just fine.
She's not only tough,
she's crafty.
♪ ♪
Hey, Mikado.
Yo, Mikado!
‐ Huh?
Hey, Seiji. Mika.
How's it going?
‐ Good.
What happened to your face?
‐ Oh. Nothing.
I took a spill down the stairs,
is all.
‐ That sucks.
Glad you're okay.
‐ Me too.
Some year, huh?
I mean, with everything
that's happened so far.
‐ Hmm? Oh.
Yeah,
and I still owe you an apology.
‐ No, don't even worry about it.
That was a crazy night
with all the Dollars there.
SEIJI: Yeah.
‐ Besides,
you guys are in the Dollars too,
so it's water under the bridge.
Got to stick together.
SEIJI: Hmm?
[Mikado chuckles]
‐ I doubt I'm ever gonna forget
that night.
Anyway, see you.
Oh, and if you guys ever get
in a jam, call me.
‐ Yeah. We will.
‐ Mikado?
‐ What?
‐ Don't break Anri's heart,
okay?
I guess
we'll see you at school, then.
‐ Yeah. Sure.
See you.
♪ ♪
‐ Mika,
he seem kind of off to you?
‐ Yup.
‐ Looked like
someone beat him up good.
And the way
he brought up the Dollars
was straight‐up weird.
‐ What do you mean?
SEIJI: I don't know.
I can't put my finger on it.
He acted like it was
something special, though.
‐ Yeah.
Oh well.
That's his deal.
No use in us worrying about it.
‐ Huh?
‐ Uh, never mind.
Come on.
Let's go eat.
‐ Okay.
♪ ♪
NAMIE: Seiji.
He's so adorable.
Even from this angle,
he's adorable.
Even when
he's with that little thief.
Mika Harima.
[tone chirping]
SHINRA: Hello?
‐ Hello, Dr. Kishitani.
It's been a long time.
SIMON: Dun‐duh!
Here is crab sushi.
It's good raw.
It's good boiled.
It's good fried.
Good people, good town,
and good taste.
They say
crab make world go round.
‐ Money
makes the world go round.
‐ Nyet.
Young person like you
should not be money‐obsessive,
but you smart.
If crab go round,
money go round.
Round and round
like merry‐go‐round.
Or sushi‐go‐round!
Da. That's good.
‐ Hey, Simon.
Who is that?
‐ Oh. That type lady
your type lady, eh?
Her name called Varona.
She be lover,
and with girlfriend,
you double‐dip.
Get her to go if want.
‐ Ridiculous.
I am under no obligation
to sell my body,
especially to improve profits
for this rathole.
I am going on strike now.
‐ [groans]
Now we sued for sex harassment.
Sex harassment no good.
Hara‐kiri for all sex harassers!
‐ I swear to God, Seiji.
You better not
be eyeballing her.
‐ Huh? Wait.
I'm confused.
Normally, you'd be all,
"I'm way hotter than her,"
and not give it
a second thought.
‐ No way.
That is so not true.
‐ But I‐‐
MAN: Mika, you have a call.
‐ Don't you think
that ringtone is kind of creepy?
‐ Are you kidding?
I love it.
[cell phone vibrating]
[phone beeps]
Hello?
NAMIE: There's something
I'd like to discuss with you,
but I don't want Seiji to know.
Would you mind
taking the call outside?
‐ Sure. Hang on a sec.
I'll be right out.
I'm sorry, Seiji.
A friend of mine wants to get
my advice about something,
so I have to go now.
‐ If you have to.
Is it Anri?
MIKA: Yeah!
She says it's important,
whatever it is.
‐ Better get going, then.
MIKA: Yep. See you tomorrow!
‐ Bye.
‐ I'm out.
NAMIE: Nice job.
I can't believe
you lie to Seiji so easily.
MIKA: If we're on the topic
of lying to Seiji,
you're the one
who changed my face to fool him.
‐ That's not quite the same
as lying.
I did that out of love.
MIKA: Huh?
‐ If you want the head,
I'll give it to you.
MIKA: What?
NAMIE: You heard me.
I want to see you alone, though.
MIKA: Do you honestly think
I'm gonna fall for that?
NAMIE: I'm sorry.
I don't know what else to do.
There's a company overseas
that wants the head.
If I give it to them,
they've offered to protect me
from the police
and from Yagiri Pharmaceuticals,
but I'd like to keep that option
as a last resort.
The other option is,
I hand over the head to Seiji,
but then I'll lose him to it,
and I want to avoid that.
That's the one thing you and I
don't want to see happen.
That's why I want to see you
today.
I'd like to get your thoughts
about what I should do,
but I don't want Seiji to know.
TOM: You got to figure out
something else, man.
You could've killed him.
Next time, try, like,
bending a coin or something.
They see that,
they'll shit their pants.
I know
you like to bust some heads,
but this is getting old.
‐ I'm sorry.
I guess
I'm not cut out for this job.
TOM: What? Hell no.
You're doing awesome.
I mean, yeah, you almost killed
that dumbass just now,
but I guess he deserved it.
I wish
I had a better gig for you.
It's dangerous out here.
I feel bad
about making you come with me.
‐ I appreciate the work.
‐ [chuckles]
What do you say
we go get us some food?
Let's do Russia Sushi
and splurge for once.
[door creaks]
[mysterious xylophone music]
‐ Anyone home?
♪ ♪
Hello‐oh?
‐ I've been waiting.
Or rather, I've made you wait,
Mika Harima.
I'm so sorry about that, really.
The dream I sold you
was an impossible one.
I'm sure it's been hard on you.
‐ Nice to see you, sis.
I guess.
‐ It's been a year
since I vanished
from Seiji's life,
and ever since then,
it's like I've been living
inside of a nightmare,
while you've been preoccupied
with your life's vicissitudes.
[chuckles]
Do you even know
what that word means?
Probably not‐‐
you don't seem like
the educated type to me.
No, you're too busy
forcing your delusions
onto Seiji.
I mean,
breaking into his apartment
and harassing him?
That doesn't sound like
the actions
of an intelligent person.
‐ I don't know why you're
unloading on me like this.
You're the reason I'm here
with this face, remember?
Not that I mind
how things turned out.
I appreciate it.
I mean, thanks to you
giving me this face,
me and Seiji can be together
forever,
and it's all 'cause of you, sis!
‐ You've got some nerve.
Who the hell
do you think you are,
calling me your sis?
And as for Seiji,
never speak his name again!
What on earth is that?
‐ What, this?
Oh, it's just a spade.
‐ Yes, I know what it is,
but I fail to see
why you would be carrying
a garden tool
in the first place.
‐ Oh. Well, I sort of figured
if I ever got my hands
on that head,
it'd come in handy.
‐ Huh?
‐ I looked all over
for something
that was the same size
and settled on a watermelon,
but what about the inside?
First,
I tried stuffing it with meat,
some tough, some not so tough.
I must've tried a hundred
different fillings, easy.
‐ Fillings? I don't follow.
‐ I needed something
that would double
as a knife and a spoon.
This spade was the perfect size.
Not sure what
a Dullahan's head tastes like,
but I can't wait to try it.
[Namie gasps]
NAMIE:
She wants to eat the head?
Seiji can't love her
as long as it's around,
but destroying the head won't
change Seiji's feelings for it.
That's why she wants to eat it.
She wants to become the head!
This changes everything.
I thought you were just a pest,
so I didn't take you seriously,
but things are different now
because I see you're my rival!
[intense orchestral music]
Plastic surgery isn't my forte,
so I'm afraid
this is going to hurt.
A lot.
SHINRA: Oh.
Oh, it's you.
Right, right, right.
Wait, I thought you were dead.
‐ I'd like to book you
for an emergency operation.
The location
is the Yagiri complex,
warehouse three.
Nebula hasn't cleared it out
yet,
so getting in
shouldn't be a problem.
SHINRA: Rush job, huh?
Did you get shot or something?
‐ No,
I need some plastic surgery done
on the girl
you worked on before.
I'd like her old face back.
Since you're familiar
with the patient already,
it shouldn't take you too long.
‐ Well, plastic surgery
doesn't quite work that way.
I can put you down
for tomorrow night, though.
NAMIE: What?
You can't do it today?
SHINRA: No. Today's my day off,
and I'm out of town.
NAMIE: Hmm. Oh well.
Too bad for her, then.
[intense periodic music]
MIKA: I'm shocked.
A crafty girl like you
should've killed me by now.
Surprise!
Move a muscle,
and you're history.
Got to hand it to you, sis.
For a girl your age,
you're fast.
‐ You are too,
although
you never really struck me
as the athletic type.
‐ Okay. Fun time's over.
Where'd you put the head?
If you don't tell me
right now... uh...
♪ ♪
Why can't I feel any...
‐ Don't worry.
This won't kill you.
I promise.
[Mika vocalizing]
Okay, lover girl.
How intimate have you been
with Seiji?
‐ That's embarrassing.
I don't talk about that stuff.
‐ I'm sure you've kissed him,
at least.
♪ ♪
[Mika gasps]
That face.
I'll be damned if I let
the taste of Seiji's lips
remain on it.
This won't kill you,
but it will scorch your face.
As punishment,
I think it's rather fitting.
Aren't you the least bit afraid?
A part of me was looking forward
to seeing that face of yours
contort in fear.
[chuckles]
Do you have any last words
before I let the acid
do its work on you?
‐ Life's vicissitudes.
That means
the ups and downs of your life.
[Namie gasps]
‐ What?
Are you sure
you want those to be
your last words?
‐ Kanra is Izaya Orihara.
Taro Tanaka is Mikado.
Setton is Celty.
Saika is Anri.
Bakyura is Masaomi.
San and Kyo
are Mairu and Kururi.
When you and Izaya trick people,
you log on to chat rooms
using the handle "Nakura."
NAMIE: No.
MIKA: Mikado
is the founder of the Dollars.
Anri is possessed
by a demon sword called Saika.
Masaomi's the leader
of the Yellow Scarves.
Although I have a feeling
they don't know
those things about each other.
Izaya Orihara hired
a couple Russians to hurt Anri.
Their names
are Sloan and Varona.
Between them, though,
Sloan's a more valuable asset
for Izaya.
Sloan told him
he was hired by the Awakusus
to kill some spies.
Izaya used that info
to frame Shizuo Heiwajima.
Then last night,
Izaya got stabbed,
and now he's in the hospital.
‐ How do you know all that?
‐ Oh, it's not too hard.
I have my tricks.
These days, bugs are super cheap
and super tiny.
The sound quality's
not too shabby either.
I found out all sorts of things,
like how
you and Izaya are playing
the Asukis and the Awakusus
off each other.
‐ You little...
What are you up to?
‐ Seiji should never know
about the bad stuff
going on around Mikado.
If he found out,
he'd want to help Mikado
'cause he still feels bad
for trying to hurt him.
He's a good person,
and I want him to stay that way.
That's why
he's never gonna find out.
This whole time,
I've been digging and digging
and digging up all the dirt
about everyone Seiji knows.
I don't want him to get dragged
into anything dangerous.
‐ [sighs]
Now I know
the kind of person you are.
You're smarter
than I gave you credit for
and even more twisted
than I ever imagined.
♪ ♪
‐ That's enough.
It's over.
NAMIE: Seiji!
MIKA: Seiji?
♪ ♪
‐ Seiji.
Oh, Seiji!
Seiji! Seiji!
‐ Ow, that hurts. Stop it.
You okay, Mika?
‐ Yeah.
‐ I don't know
what's going on with you guys,
but this is going too far,
and it's got to stop, okay?
‐ But...
how did you know we were here?
‐ I ran into Anri
on my way home.
I asked her
if she'd spoken to Mika today.
She said she hadn't.
I tried calling
but kept getting her voice mail.
Then I called everyone we knew.
‐ Yeah.
Go to the Yagiri complex,
and she's in warehouse three.
Sorry I can't chat.
I'm a little busy now. Bye!
‐ That four‐eyed rat.
[Mika gasps]
♪ ♪
‐ See? Now you know
what it must have felt like
for Mika
when you did that to her.
[Namie panting]
[Namie cries out]
‐ Hey, wait.
Where'd you put the head?
Why won't she tell me?
MIKA:
Well, maybe she doesn't know
where it is anymore.
‐ Really?
Then you think
maybe that Izaya Orihara guy
you were talking about has it?
‐ I broke into
all three of his apartments
and checked the closets,
the cupboards‐‐
you name it.
I couldn't find it anywhere.
‐ Oh, well.
At least you tried.
‐ Yeah.
SEIJI: I think it's time
you stopped breaking into
people's homes, though.
MIKA: Okay.
‐ Can you stand up?
MIKA: Nope.
♪ ♪
‐ If you found the head first,
what were you gonna do with it?
‐ I'd eat it.
‐ Why?
‐ It'd be part of me then.
If that happened, you'd fall
in love with me for sure.
♪ ♪
‐ No, I wouldn't.
‐ Why not?
‐ 'Cause I'd stop you
before you ate it.
‐ Even if you had to kill me?
‐ Yeah.
‐ That's my Seiji.
‐ Seiji.
♪ ♪
[giggling]
[laughing loudly]
♪ ♪
MIKA: You know, Seiji,
you don't know
a thing about women.
I mean, you go on and on
about how much you love
that darn head,
and then, like some big tease,
you have to go and kiss
your sister.
‐ I didn't.
‐ Huh?
‐ When I leaned in,
I put my fingers up
between our lips like this,
so technically, I didn't.
‐ That's still pretty cruel.
‐ Really?
‐ Mm‐hmm.
Don't play
with a girl's emotions.
♪ ♪
["Exit" by Revalcy]
[man singing in Japanese]
♪ ♪
The man has a scar
and a past
and principles to stick to
and a red light
burning inside his right eye.
Next time‐‐
"Marriages Are Made in Heaven."