["Headhunt" by Okamoto's]
[man singing in Japanese]
♪ ♪
‐ The reward is...
BAKYURA: 10 mil?!
MAN:
Let's get our 10 million yen!
‐ Heh. Celty?
Yeah, I might know something.
‐ You do know something,
don't you?
That's not fair!
SHINGEN: I hired him
to apprehend a certain woman.
SHINRA: A woman?
‐ Think positive.
He's a monster
who wants to become human.
‐ Yah!
‐ Huh?
♪ ♪
‐ [sighs]
An arm.
An arm?
Wait, that's an arm, right?
Ah, jeez.
It's a corpse!
Great. Now what do I do?
MAN: Get back here!
‐ You losers want
the 10 million yen that bad?
Just put away 50,000 a month
for 200 months!
[Cóiste‐Bodhar neighs]
MAN: What's with
the damn magic tricks?
‐ Just look at that!
The Black Rider is driving
on the walls of the buildings!
And the number of bikers
after the bounty
is increasing by the second.
Will we finally get to see
who the mysterious rider is?
MAN:
Find out after this commercial‐‐
♪ ♪
‐ So, uh, you guys are serious?
You're really with
the Yellow Scarves?
‐ Hey, don't sweat it.
It's not like we care
what you were doing
at the factory.
‐ We just want to get
the 10 million yen
that's up for grabs,
you get what I'm saying?
‐ You know
where the Black Rider is,
so don't try to play us!
‐ Start off
by giving us your cell phone.
Bet you anything
it's got the Rider's number.
‐ Let go!
‐ Huh?
Who in the hell are‐‐
‐ Damn it, you‐‐
‐ Whoa! It's Kyohei!
‐ Hurry up, and get in, guys!
[tires screeching]
‐ Damn you, bastard!
‐ Piss off.
‐ [sighs]
Thanks. That was close.
‐ Ah, it was nothing, really.
Sorry we were late
for hooking up with you.
‐ Hold on. You guys?
What are you doing here?
‐ [giggles]
‐ Why is everyone acting crazy?
What the heck's going on?
‐ Well, to be honest,
afraid we got some bad news
for you guys.
We may have gotten you
out of one disaster,
but we ended dragging you
into another one.
Right now,
this area is a trouble zone,
like a certain Academy City
where everyone studies
supernatural powers.
‐ Are you sure
you're feeling all right?
‐ There's been
a lot of stuff going down.
No big.
‐ Stuff? What kind of stuff?
[Cóiste‐Bodhar neighs]
ALL: Huh?
‐ I should never have
taken this job.
I haven't been thinking straight
since I lost that money.
‐ I'd like you to hold on
to this bag.
It'll only be for one day.
We can't have anyone finding it.
Just hang onto it
till this time tomorrow.
Then you can dump it.
‐ Excuse me,
but who referred you to me?
‐ An information broker.
Izaya Orihara.
‐ Ugh. Now I get it.
This smells really fishy.
Sorry, but I'm a transporter.
If you need a safe‐deposit box,
try a bank.
‐ Maybe this'll
change your mind.
[cash register cha‐chings]
‐ I'd be happy to do it!
[men yelling]
What do I do if the police come?
Whatever. I don't care.
I just don't want Shinra and I
to live apart... Shinra...
[Cóiste‐Bodhar whickers]
No. This isn't good.
Get a hold of yourself!
You can do this!
It's gonna work out! Huh?
That's...
‐ The Black Rider?
‐ Celty!
‐ It is Celty!
‐ Hey, now Celty's here!
‐ What's going on here, Mikado?
‐ [gasps] Look!
It's the Black Rider, Kururi!
The Black Rider!
‐ Okay.
CELTY: Sorry.
Bikers are chasing me. Run!
‐ Hate to tell you this‐‐
afraid we're the ones
who stirred 'em up.
[men yelling]
‐ Gah!
‐ We do have one thing
in our favor.
None of those bikers are locals,
while most of us here in the van
are members of the Dollars.
They want to mess around
on our turf,
we have every right
to kick their asses.
Punch it.
‐ You bet.
[men yelling]
‐ [gasps]
What do we do now?
Think we should call the police?
‐ I'm sure that someone's
already called 'em.
Don't sweat it.
I'll see that nothing happens
to you high schoolers.
‐ Right.
‐ Are you feeling all right,
Mikado?
‐ Y‐yeah. It's all good.
Sorry.
Wish they could let you two off.
‐ That's not what I‐‐
forget it.
It's no big deal.
CELTY: So many things
have happened in this past year.
I met Mikado and the others,
joined the Dollars,
became friends with Anri,
and most importantly, Shinra.
‐ What? Yuma,
your definition of tsundere
is way too narrow, like toast.
‐ Celty doesn't
fit the mold,
since she's honest
but can't be totally cold.
She's more of
a big sister type character
who'd take care of others
in the good old days.
Like the one
who lets herself be coddled
by an unreliable big brother.
Right! She's a big‐‐
‐ Shinra, since those guys
came into our home,
they haven't stopped
talking about me.
What's up with that?
‐ Yeah,
I suppose you're gonna find out,
so I might as well tell you.
I ran into them at a bar
earlier,
and they were all talking about
how amazing you are,
and things kind of slipped out.
I had to brag
that you were my girlfriend
and gush over this and that,
like
everything we did on our dates
and some other details.
Yeah, alcohol's a scary thing.
Stop it.
Ow. Ow. Ow.
What are you doing, Celty?
Maybe you really are tsundere.
Ow. Ow. Ow. Ow. Ow!
CELTY:
The truth is, I was so happy.
I've been jumping for joy
this year.
Almost too happy.
Considering all that,
well, I can't just‐‐
I can't just give it up now!
‐ Serious?
Gotcha.
You know, considering
everything we've been through,
we've never really been
formally introduced,
so I hope you won't think I'm
out of line here, but listen.
I want a chance to pay you back,
Celty, okay?
[horn sounding]
Hmm?
[men yelling]
‐ Hmm?
[grunting and yelling]
[men yelling]
♪ ♪
[horns sounding]
[men yelling]
‐ All right.
Get out, and make a run for it.
ALL: Huh?
‐ Okay,
but what are you gonna do?
‐ Well, the way I see it,
Celty's a lady.
At least she looks like one,
anyway.
Wouldn't you agree, Saburo?
‐ Huh? Yeah, sure.
‐ We couldn't call ourselves
gentlemen
if we left a lady at the mercy
of those thugs, right?
‐ Right.
[tires screeching]
‐ Hey, Aoba, take care of Anri
and those two girls.
‐ What? Mikado, wait!
Where did Anri go?
‐ What now?
‐ [sighs]
Guess
we'll have to wait and see.
Who knows
what's gonna happen next?
But can you believe
we got such a close‐up look?
I mean, think about it‐‐
wouldn't it be cool
if we actually
got to meet Celty?
‐ What the hell?
[men grunt]
‐ Damn it.
They're coming back?
I told them to run. Huh?
‐ You can leave them all to me.
You should make your escape.
CELTY: Mikado!
Anri!
[man grunting]
Who's that?
Wait.
I know that aura.
It's...
This morning's client.
‐ Please let me pay you back
for your services.
‐ Holy crap.
What the hell's going on?
‐ Hurry.
Please go look after Mother.
‐ Mother?
Saika.
I'll leave things to you
if you insist.
My friends are‐‐
no, I'm in danger.
I'll give you two pieces
of advice to thank you.
First, run from any motorcycle
officers you see.
There's a monster
in their ranks!
Secondly,
don't ever pick a fight
with anyone dressed
as a bartender.
No matter what.
SHIZUO:
Bunch of damn petty thieves!
BOTH: Huh?
‐ Ah!
‐ Damn it. We can't go home
after taking that beatdown.
The boss'll kill us
when he hears about this.
‐ We got to at least flex
a little muscle
and put the fear of God
into the local gang, right?
‐ Hey, Rasta Boy,
I got a question for you.
What's the name
of the baddest gang around here,
and where can we find 'em?
‐ Are you guys trying to pick
a fight with 'em or something?
‐ What do you think?
‐ Toramaru from Saitama, right?
Your gang's boss
is a ladies' man,
but I've also heard that
he doesn't put up with any crap.
He's not gonna be down
with what you guys are planning.
‐ Why don't you
shut the hell up,
you dreadlocked piece of‐‐
‐ What the hell, man?
My shirt.
My little brother gave
this shirt to me.
You guys are dead!
[men yelling]
‐ It's tranquil today
in the city.
Oh. There was some news
on that reward for Celty.
It's been cancelled
after a police reprimand.
Still,
I hear that CEO's in a good mood
since they got
Ruri Hijiribe's contract.
‐ Why, it's fabulous!
How about a round of applause,
people?
Celebrate!
This is a happy occasion,
one I've got no problem
accepting,
even with this scandal,
which is why I'm giving you two
my blessing here and now.
[laughing]
IZAYA: Her old agency
has been shut down,
since it seems their CEO,
Yodogiri, has gone missing.
‐ Well, the rest is up
to our young couple over here.
Us old fogies can go home.
‐ The events that led up
to Hollywood discovering
she had powers,
the reason
that she became a serial killer,
what happened back then,
and what Yodogiri did to me‐‐
I haven't told you
any of that yet.
‐ If you don't want to say,
then you shouldn't
force yourself.
‐ To tell the truth,
I would like you to hear it.
‐ No, thanks.
I'm sure that once you tell me,
that's it.
You'll end it all.
Everyone can clearly see
how I am.
Since I can't share
people's feelings,
I thought that I should
at least try my best
to understand them,
so I've been observing people
closely.
That's why I have a pretty good
idea of what you're thinking.
I'd prefer it
if you didn't die, Ruri,
so I don't want you
to tell me anything.
‐ You know something?
I think you might be
some kind of monster after all.
But hear me out,
because ever since I was young,
I felt the need
to destroy everything I touched,
and yet, the fear of losing
those closest to me
outweighed that need.
I couldn't become a monster
completely
unless I destroyed myself,
but in the end, I think
the thought of losing myself
was the one thing
I was most frightened of.
‐ The fear of losing something.
Sounds to me
like you might consider that
another kind of love.
There's something
that I never told you.
‐ And what's that?
‐ When you pushed me down
on the bed
and got on top of me, I think
that moment got me
extremely flustered.
‐ Huh?
‐ My heart started beating
very quickly,
and my chest felt hot.
‐ Is that your way
of winning me over?
‐ I was only explaining
the facts.
‐ Well, that side of you‐‐
it's kind of charming.
♪ ♪
‐ After purchasing
all these clothes,
you're still not done shopping?
‐ Not quite yet.
‐ You're in no position
to complain, Egor.
We put up the money
to pay your entire medical bill,
and you ended up letting
Celty get away just like that.
IZAYA:
The twins were on a mission.
They wanted to meet Celty
no matter what.
They got some information
from a certain source
that the envelope was addressed
to a transporter
on a black bike.
In return
for paying the medical bills,
they asked Russia Sushi for help
in putting on a little show.
The head chef was to contact
Celty while in disguise.
Egor was to hide inside a bag
that Celty would transport
and,
once he reached her hideout,
contact my sisters
via cell phone.
At least, that was the plan.
Naturally, a scheme like that
would never work out.
But the 1 million yen
they found on the street
ultimately did make its way
back to Celty,
so I guess you could say
those two actually did
a rare good deed.
‐ Hey, Egor,
you were the one who ended up
beating the snot out
of those bikers
at the underpass, weren't you?
I knew
you had to be someone special,
but you've got to be
a Russian super soldier
to pull off something like that.
‐ You're amazing.
‐ No. That other person deserves
the credit.
IZAYA: In reality,
Egor's known to be
the seventh most feared hit man
in Russia.
Also known as the
"Philosophical Killing Machine."
Well,
if anything did happen with him,
it would be their problem,
not mine.
Now, as for what's going on
with Celty...
‐ All right, guys.
Make sure you pay attention,
now.
For sagohachi‐style pickles,
the quality of the malted rice
and the ratio you use
is what makes or breaks
this dish.
So we start off
with this bed of sagohachi
that I brought from home,
and it's fully fermented.
‐ I'm home. Hey,
what the heck's going on here?
‐ Since I'm between jobs now,
I thought it'd be a good time
to learn how to cook.
I went to ask Anri
for lessons first,
but it seems
she's not a very good cook.
Then I tried
to get Erika to teach me,
but Japanese cuisine
wasn't her thing.
This is who Anri brought over.
♪ ♪
ALL: [gasp]
‐ She can really cook, huh?
‐ I think most would say
she's top‐notch,
which means she's
super top‐notch in my book.
‐ You're such a flatterer,
aren't you?
Okay. Now you just lay them
in the bed of sagohachi
and let them pickle all night.
‐ All night?
‐ Yep. All night.
‐ No shortcuts?
‐ No shortcuts.
‐ What now?
We've got nothing for dinner.
‐ Hmm.
Hot pot!
CELTY: Hot pot?
‐ Yeah, and while we're at it,
let's invite all our friends!
We're going to have ourselves
a hot pot party.
[all voicing agreement]
‐ Open wide!
So good!
[giggling]
‐ Mm‐hmm.
‐ Shouldn't you eat?
‐ Well, it's like this.
Just seeing
the smile on your face
is enough to keep me going.
‐ That's a bit much.
But thanks.
‐ Oh, man. These last few days
have been pretty tough,
haven't they?
‐ Yeah.
It makes me wonder
if I'm really doing
the right thing.
‐ How so?
‐ I'm just trying to figure out
if being a transporter
is the best job for me.
‐ And what brought this up
all of a sudden?
‐ It's just, whenever
I take on a dangerous job,
even if I'm okay with the risk,
it causes trouble for you, and‐‐
‐ We're family, Celty.
A little trouble means nothing.
And as long as I've got
you by my side,
whatever comes, it'll never
feel like trouble to me.
‐ Shinra...
‐ And besides,
I overcame
the greatest obstacle of all‐‐
winning your love.
Oh.
[chuckles]
TARO: By the way,
I was at a hot pot party
with my friends today.
SETTON: What a coincidence.
So was I.
KANRA: What? Hot pot?
At this time of year?
KYO: Oh, what a coincidence.
We were enjoying
some shabu‐shabu ourselves
a little earlier today.
SAN: It was good.
IZAYA: Kururi, Mairu‐‐
I know it's you.
How did you find this address?
KURURI:
Ms. Namie was kind enough
to point us
in the right direction.
Other brother.
IZAYA/MAIRU:
Do you even have friends
who will join you for hot pot?
‐ He asks.
‐ How mean.
KURURI:
I'd greatly appreciate it
if you wouldn't intrude
into the friendships
of young ladies,
brother, dear.
KURURI/IZAYA: It's a secret.
IZAYA: Hmm? Use privacy mode.
Better yet, get out of here,
you two.
BAKYURA: I went to have sukiyaki
with a female friend of mine.
Just the two of us.
You heard of these places?
All‐you‐can‐eat sukiyaki joints
that charge around 1,500 yen?
TARO: Oh, yeah.
There's a whole chain of 'em.
SAIKA:
I had hot pot with Setton.
It was delicious.
KANRA: I swear!
You guys have no sense
of the seasons.
You're only supposed to eat
hot pot style dishes
in the winter!
‐ Do you have any plans?
‐ For what?
‐ Thought I'd treat you
to some hot pot.
Shabu‐shabu, or maybe some crab.
You can choose
whatever you want.
‐ Because your little chat room
friends are having hot pot?
If you're looking for someone
to soothe your injured vanity,
you should try a therapist.
‐ Hmm?
You read that?
Namie, it wasn't you
who happened to tell my sisters
about Celty, now, was it?
‐ Who knows?
I couldn't really say.
‐ [laughs]
You've turned into a force
to be reckoned with,
haven't you?
‐ Still,
I've discovered one thing.
‐ And that is?
‐ That life goes on,
even without your involvement.
And no one invited you
to have hot pot,
so I guess you aren't
the center of the universe.
‐ [laughs]
All I did
was make an observation
of how some others
spent their day off.
But I think it's about time
I start enjoying
my own days off.
After all, there are
potential sparks everywhere.
ANRI: I didn't realize.
‐ Forgive the intrusion,
my lovely young lady.
‐ To think
Saika would act on its own.
If...if Saika had stabbed
Mikado and Masaomi
the same way‐‐
SAIKA: I love you...
I love you...
I love you...I love you...
‐ Nothing? Still haven't had
any luck finding Yodogiri?
‐ Looks like
the other organizations
are starting to think
we offed him ourselves.
‐ That sly old dog.
I can't believe he joined forces
with multiple groups.
‐ We can't let our guard down.
‐ This guy's way too sketchy.
I don't believe for a minute
this bullshit
about being a talent agency CEO.
‐ We got to get
the goods on this guy.
No matter what it costs,
we're gonna make sure
we bury that con artist dead.
‐ That Mikado.
He's interesting,
that's for sure.
No doubt about that.
I told you about that time
the bikers were after him,
right?
I mean, the situation
was just dripping with danger.
Anyone else
would've broke down and cried.
But he didn't flinch.
Even with all that pressure.
He loves
those surreal situations,
like stuff
straight out of some comic book.
It's almost unbelievable.
He thrives on it,
and that's exactly
the kind of guy he is.
See what I mean?
That's why
Mikado started the Dollars
in the first place.
‐ I'm not sure I get it.
‐ Sounds like
Mikado's just trying
to keep from getting bored.
‐ Things got interesting
when the feud between
the Yellow Scarves and Dollars
was heating up.
It'd be lame if it ended without
much damage to either gang.
‐ So,
you want to make a new spark
and have 'em start a fight, huh?
‐ Yeah, but even if we did,
there's someone
catching those sparks
and using them
for his own reasons.
Got to deal with that hyena
first.
Izaya Orihara has got to go.
Oh, but not the twins.
Nobody lays a hands
on Izaya's sisters, okay?
I got a thing for those two.
They kind of kissed me
out of the blue,
know what I mean?
‐ Oh, give me a break, Izumi.
‐ Never use my old name.
It reminds me
of my scumbag brother.
IZAYA: What I'm trying to do
is gather those sparks
and toss them all in one place,
and then
I'm going to say to them,
"Your vacation's over.
You piece of shit."
[man singing in Japanese]
NAMIE: It's so asinine.
I wonder why the world
is teeming with such fools.
Who needs him?
Or him? Or him?
All I need is my Seiji.
Still...next time‐‐
"No One Knows
What the Future Holds."