["Headhunt" by Okamoto's]
[man singing in Japanese]
♪ ♪
[tires squeal]
VARONA: Job was too easy.
Black Rider was beyond feeble.
‐ Kill or be killed.
Both very bad.
SHINRA: Did you kidnap a kid?
‐ And what I'd like you to do
is capture her.
Preferably alive
if at all possible.
IZAYA: Didn't that thing
with the yellow scarves
teach you anything?
I heard that it created a rift
between you and that
former best friend of yours.
[man singing in Japanese]
♪ ♪
‐ Come! Russia Sushi!
It's sushi!
Hey, young lady,
how would you like
to make your skin nice and tight
with fresh fish?
Enjoy big feast together.
Have sushi night fever.
Sound good?
‐ [speaking Russian]
‐ Hmm?
‐ Da.
[accordion music]
‐ Hey, boss,
I find good customer.
Hungry for Russia Sushi, okay?
MAN: [speaking Russian]
EGOR: ...Two types of Ivans
among Russian men.
First, there's the Ivan
who's too married to his job,
like a machine.
The other
is the unorthodox Ivan
who's got a screw loose
in his head.
[animal howls]
♪ ♪
‐ This not make sense.
No sense at all.
DRAKON: Tell me,
Comrade Lingerin,
what is that troubles you?
LINGERIN: Look, Drakon.
Look at this.
DRAKON: Look at what?
‐ Cannot remove hands from jars.
‐ I see.
That is cause for alarm.
‐ I was trying
to get at what was inside
when hands got stuck.
‐ Let's get back to the matter
at hand, Comrade Lingerin.
[dramatic music]
LINGERIN: What is
we were talking about, Comrade?
DRAKON: We were talking
about Varona and Sloan.
LINGERIN: Of course.
That was it.
These stupid bastards
interrupted us.
They were clueless,
so they end up dead.
Not like Dennis and Simon.
Always read situation correctly.
Those two chose perfect time
to run away.
We attacked rival weapons house,
and they run
before enemy retaliate.
[laughs]
‐ It's as if the predicament
with your hands is a metaphor
for our current situation,
Comrade Lingerin.
‐ You think I enjoy
having these things on my hands.
‐ [grunts]
[gunshots]
‐ Of course.
I just had to fire the gun.
‐ [groans]
[gunshots]
‐ If you were willing
to break it with a bullet,
perhaps you should have
just smashed it to begin with.
Or simply released the gun
so you could withdraw your hand.
Perhaps real question is,
why put guns in vases
in first place?
‐ I don't understand
a single word you are saying.
Speak Russian, Comrade.
DRAKON:
If words I uttered moments ago
sounded like English
or Japanese,
then is very possible
that one of us
has damaged Wernicke's area,
which is part of brain
that controls comprehension.
In which case, bol'nitsa
is place we should be.
Who gets shipped to sanatoriy
is what I am anxious to see.
‐ [blubbers]
So we were talking
about little Varona.
‐ It sickens me,
but they have broken
the most sacrosanct
of our unwritten laws.
If I could,
I would use my bare hands
to litter the ground
with their brain matter.
‐ Is a bit harsh, considering
she is your daughter.
I think
we would be better served
if we simply found some place
to lock them up for a while.
‐ Lock them away?
Starvation is far more
painful demise than shooting.
LINGERIN: You miss the point.
Do not kill them.
It is not like we're
the army or the mafia.
Besides, you could never capture
and execute Varona anyway.
‐ I see your point.
It's a shame that
I can't lay a finger on her.
Which is exactly
why I sent Egor to Japan,
instructing him
to ask Dennis and Simon
for help if necessary,
but Egor had an encounter
with one of the locals
the other day
and sustained serious injuries.
LINGERIN: Who knew Japan
is such dangerous place?
Maybe Egor run into judo
or karate master.
Ah, I shoot vase off.
‐ Just friendly advice,
if I may,
but might consider breaking it
with gun's grip to avoid injury.
‐ Hmm...
[soft dramatic music]
DRAKON: Once she learns
that Egor suffered defeat
at the hands of a local,
I'm sure Varona
will take action.
LINGERIN: [grunts]
[vase shatters]
You're right.
Little Varona has human side.
Unlike her father,
who is more like machine.
She is quick to kill people
out of instinct
or to satisfy her desires.
‐ I know you have
your own theories about her,
but as a person,
Varona is still immature.
The one thing she does have
is knowledge
due to all the books
at her disposal,
but mentally,
she's a child.
‐ Here.
Is good the brats
are talking it out
in foreign country, but...
[fire whooshes,
glass shatters]
They made off
with too many of our toys,
which are not for kids.
♪ ♪
EGOR: I'll say it again.
There are only two types
of Ivans among Russian men.
Both types tend not to be good
at reading situations.
And there's tonight's
guest of honor...
the beautiful assassin
named Varona,
which means "crow" in Russian.
She has inherited traits from
each of the two types of Ivans:
a machine‐like accuracy
and a human appetite
for destruction.
And yet, she's far better
at reading a situation
than them.
At least until now.
‐ With that new look of yours,
you'd be right at home
on the big screen, Egor.
EGOR: You think the ladies
will dig me?
‐ Hmm.
Don't you think
it's about time
you filled me in?
You came a long way
from Russia.
What's the guy known as
the "Philosophical
Killing Machine" doing in Japan?
Ah, shit.
You aren't here to kill us
after all this time, are you?
EGOR:
The colonel has no intention
of doing anything
to either of you.
I'm here for
the two other deserters.
Ones who made off with a number
of the company's
anti‐material rifles.
‐ Anti‐material rifles?
You gotta be kidding.
That is some
seriously dangerous stuff
they walked off with.
SIMON: You can't eat danger,
but you can do the Awa Dance.
Always let
sleeping sushi insects lie.
‐ So who are
these two deserters?
EGOR: Their code names
are Varona and Sloan.
DENNIS:
A crow and an elephant, huh?
Hmm, I don't know
this Sloan character,
but I remember Varona.
‐ Yes, she is Drakon's
little girl.
EGOR: That's right,
but she's no longer
the same person
that you once knew.
DENNIS:
No matter what she's become,
she's still our little girl.
Even the colonel would say so.
EGOR: Considering
Lingerin's relationship to her,
that's probably true.
Regardless,
there are indications
that the two of them
have entered the Ikebukuro area.
I figured you should know
so you could be ready.
‐ Is this your way of asking us
to help catch them?
EGOR:
That's not what I was implying,
but having them
cause a scene here
would be bad for business.
If you know what I mean.
‐ Yeah, right.
But I'm sure the young miss
can read the lay of the land
well enough to know
she can't fire
that thing off around here.
Not unless she was
in a real crisis or something.
EGOR: I certainly hope so.
[door closes]
[both sigh]
♪ ♪
EGOR: The young girl grew up
without affection
from her father,
and her father, who was given
the code name Drakon,
didn't even try
to connect with her.
Instead, he only gave her books
to pass the time.
She devoured all kinds of books
at several times the speed
of average people
and drove everything
into her head,
from information
relevant to life
to useless trivia,
fact after fact.
Aware that
her father was involved
in some kind
of unsavory business,
the parents in the neighborhood
made sure they kept their kids
away from her.
Her childhood was a lonely one,
but she was content
as long as she had her books.
Until that one moment
in time...
♪ ♪
[glass shatters]
‐ [gasps]
‐ Hmm?
‐ [breathing heavily]
‐ [exhales]
♪ ♪
MAN: Come out, come out,
wherever you are.
Little girl?
‐ [whimpering]
‐ [growls]
[water running]
♪ ♪
[chuckles softly]
Huh?
‐ [grunts]
[both grunt]
MAN: [shouts]
[coughs, sputters]
[breathing heavily]
[hair dryer blowing]
[exhales sharply]
[gasps]
[shouts]
♪ ♪
‐ [gasps]
EGOR: The night she used
the knowledge
she'd acquired in books
to kill a burglar in her home,
the moment she looked upon
the body that had stopped moving
more quickly
than she could have imagined,
a strange kind of breeze
blew within her heart.
♪ ♪
"My cold, machine‐like father
acknowledges me.
"At this moment,
he is trying to connect with me.
"Why? What have I done?"
YOUNG VARONA:
Because I took out the bad guy?
Because I killed someone
stronger than me?
Because I was strong?
Probably not.
But still...
EGOR: The men didn't intend
to teach her techniques
that were meant
for killing people.
[exciting music]
SIMON: [grunting]
‐ [grunting]
EGOR: But since it was necessary
to teach her self‐defense,
they had no choice
but to show her
some of the basic techniques.
♪ ♪
[both grunt]
‐ [groans]
♪ ♪
EGOR: The young girl then turned
those moves she'd learned
into ways
she could defeat others.
She started with thugs
in the city.
Her next targets
were armed drug dealers.
And, finally,
professional mercenaries.
‐ [exhales sharply]
[both grunt]
EGOR: Three of them.
Five.
[gunshot]
Six.
♪ ♪
And then one day,
after gaining information
about a group
that had been antagonizing
her father's company,
she made her way to their base
without telling her father
and eliminated them all.
[footsteps approaching]
[all breathing heavily]
♪ ♪
[both grunt]
EGOR: She wasn't a fool.
She had to have known
there was no way
her father would praise her
for such an act.
Then why did she do
such a thing?
The answer was simple.
YOUNG VARONA: "It was fun."
"It was fun."
[doorbell rings]
‐ [grunts]
[exhales]
[gasps]
[grunts]
[dramatic jazz music]
VARONA: Relax.
I won't kill you.
You won't be able to move
for a few days.
Perhaps a few months, possibly.
However, there is no need
for you to die.
You should consider yourself
fortunate.
MIKADO:
No, that's not true at all.
Masaomi's still my friend.
Even now.
‐ Wouldn't it be nice
if he reciprocated that feeling?
MIKADO: What's that mean?
‐ Nothing really.
I'm probably just being jealous
since you boys are out there
enjoying your youth and all.
You see, I never had
that kind of friendship myself.
Just a pervert I can't ditch
and a violent moron I hate.
But never mind that.
Getting back on topic,
as one of its founders,
whether you like it or not,
the Dollars have
some degree of power.
If you obliterate
those around you,
you'd not only increase
the gang's profile,
you'd naturally rise
in the ranks.
Unfortunately,
there are some people
with that kind of mind‐set.
‐ Yeah, I see what you mean.
‐ Don't worry.
All you have to do
is keep quiet
and you'll get through this.
What's important to the Dollars?
Freedom.
Am I right?
It's all about the freedom.
So from that standpoint,
the concept of the Dollars
makes it
an even bigger category
than a color gang
or something like that.
I mean, you couldn't call it
a nation or a tribe,
but it's big enough to have
good guys and bad guys in it.
MIKADO: Right.
IZAYA: Let me show you
what I'm getting at.
Now, hypothetically,
let's say that you wanted
to stop the Dollars
from attacking someone
and actually managed to do it.
It wouldn't be
the Dollars anymore.
If you can bend the whole group
to your single will,
then it turns into
something entirely different.
You founded the Dollars
as a joke online,
but when members started tagging
and pulling crap in real life,
you wanted to do something
about it, didn't you?
You must have hated
feeling so helpless.
‐ Of course.
Anyone would.
IZAYA:
If you really felt that way,
then why would you want
to keep the Dollars going?
It would have been better
to forget about it instead
or choose to drop out.
‐ That'd be irresponsible!
IZAYA: It's all about freedom.
The Dollars don't expect you
to take responsibility,
but if that's
something you want,
you're a hell of a lot more
conscientious than I thought.
Although I'm pretty sure
it's not your moral fortitude
that keeps you going.
‐ What the hell
are you talking about?
IZAYA: What you're afraid of
isn't the group
spinning out of control.
‐ Huh?
IZAYA: It's obvious
the Dollars are transforming
and you're scared as hell
you're going to get left behind.
‐ This is sad day.
Asking us to torment young girl
like this,
is more like job for random thug
from street corner.
[Cóiste‐Bodhar neighs faintly]
Huh?
What is strange sound
out window?
[Cóiste‐Bodhar neighs]
Could be a horse?
What is horse doing in city?
[Cóiste‐Bodhar neighs]
[thinking]
Is crazy. Makes no sense.
[exciting music]
[Cóiste‐Bodhar neighs]
[gasps]
[speaks Russian]
‐ I'm sorry.
You'll have to forgive me,
but I have no idea who you are.
You may have the wrong person.
VARONA: What?
Looks like ordinary girl.
‐ If you're
some sort of burglar...
VARONA: What is she?
‐ I don't keep any cash
in the house.
VARONA: I should get out.
SAIKI: Please leave.
VARONA: But my body,
it's moving on its own.
I'm going to die.
♪ ♪
[exhales shakily]
What will happen if I'm cut?
What is this girl?
Is she human?
I remember... something hot.
This is like back then.
YOUNG VARONA:
I'm going to be killed.
I'm going to kill.
I can kill.
♪ ♪
VARONA: I've always wanted
to see it for myself
since that day.
How fragile humans are.
Even me.
Are we really so fragile?
What will happen
if this sword cuts my flesh?
I'm consumed
by the impulse to find out.
I can't control the urge.
[truck horn honking]
[grunts]
The signal.
You're mysterious and bizarre.
I will come back, my dear.
It was pleasure to meet you.
[grunts]
[Cóiste‐Bodhar neighs]
What?
♪ ♪
Punch it!
‐ With pleasure.
[tires squeal, engine revs]
♪ ♪
[grunting]
‐ [gasps]
[Cóiste‐Bodhar neighs]
♪ ♪
No way!
This is monstrous!
‐ What in hell is this?
‐ [grunts]
Is crisis.
♪ ♪
[Cóiste‐Bodhar neighing]
[speaking Russian]
[weapon fires,
explosion roars]
‐ Hmm?
EGOR: [grunts]
‐ [gasps softly]
[tires squeal]
VARONA: Sloan, what happened
to the Black Rider?
SLOAN: I don't know.
One second,
I can see Black Rider on monitor
and then big flash
and rider is gone.
Please tell me you did not
use that thing, Varona.
‐ I had to.
We were in a crisis.
[exhales sharply]
There should be
an abandoned factory nearby.
Take us there.
‐ [exhales]
What is your plan?
‐ It appears
the bike was marked somehow.
I intend to dump it.
Or perhaps we can use it
as a lure for an ambush.
‐ [breathing heavily]
[Cóiste‐Bodhar neighs]
CELTY: You've gotta be careful.
‐ [gasps]
[soft dramatic piano music]
‐ Well, it's just‐‐
I nearly got shot.
I shielded myself
with an incredibly thick
wall of shadows,
but I still got pushed
all the way here.
[weapon fires]
Or rather,
I was blown all this way.
Yeah, I think it was
a really close call.
Poor Shooter
was almost pulverized.
[Cóiste‐Bodhar chuffs]
Why did they target you?
‐ I wish I knew.
I have no idea what's going on.
Do you think that
she'll be coming back?
CELTY: It's all right.
You can stay over
at my place tonight.
ANRI: I couldn't.
CELTY: Please.
Don't worry about it.
You've spent the night
at our house before.
Besides, we should
come up with a strategy
to fight whoever they are.
‐ Thank you, Celty.
‐ By the way,
you wouldn't happen to have
a mask or a helmet, would you?
I was careless
and left mine on the street
and when I went back for it...
A dump truck ran over it
and ruined it.
I'll have to go back
for a spare otherwise.
♪ ♪
‐ Hold on.
I remember
that you made a helmet
out of your shadows
for me once,
so couldn't you
do the same thing?
[air puffs]
‐ I didn't think of that.
♪ ♪
MIKADO:
Geez, I couldn't sleep at all.
IZAYA: You're a good person,
and that's something
to be respected,
but didn't you start the Dollars
because you got bored
of being respectable?
An escape from the ordinary.
Isn't that your dream?
[keys clacking]
That's why
I'm worried about you.
MIKADO: [sighs]
IZAYA: I said it before,
didn't I?
To enjoy an ordinary life,
you have to constantly evolve,
but that's definitely not
something
you should try to do
by yourself.
MIKADO: Yeah, but, Orihara‐‐
IZAYA: Call me Izaya.
MIKADO: Oh, okay.
IZAYA: Don't forget,
you have plenty of allies
out there willing to help.
There's Anri, Kida, even me.
If there's anything I can do,
then I'll help you
however I can.
I just wanted
to let you know that.
MIKADO: Um, Izaya...
IZAYA: What is it?
MIKADO: Thank you.
I mean it.
♪ ♪
Izaya,
I always thought
he was so sketchy,
but he's nice.
[knocks on door]
EGOR: As with Ivans in Russia,
there are two different types
of Taros among Japanese men.
The kind yet naive Taro...
‐ Oh.
EGOR: And the Taro
who uses such people.
And both of them tend
to read more into a situation
than they should.
‐ [laughs softly]
["Never Say Never"
by Three Lights Down Kings]
[man singing in Japanese]
♪ ♪
MASAOMI: Listen to my tale
about a worthless guy.
One who's driven
by conspiracies,
schemes, and violence.
He's serious as hell,
and 'cause of that,
he's about to screw up.
Next time, "The Ladies' Man
Has Neither Money Nor Power."