♪ [singing in Japanese]
-[people exclaiming]
-[tires squealing]
[Masaomi]
He's crazy.
If you're dumb enough to grab
me, hang on for the ride!
Izumii!
[Yodogiri]
I don't know what happened.
I thought if he
hurt him bad enough,
he would go berserk.
♪ [singing continues]
Uh.
I'm pleased to meet you.
My name is Kasane Kujiragi.
Who?
[Varona]
In city, far away
from Mother Russia,
after become acquainted
with strangers,
I wonder, have I changed?
Doctor,
I'm interested in you.
Huh?
Mm--
[Celty]
Saika.
Wait. What's happening?
What am I seeing?
A Saika-wielder?
Infidelity?
No. It's Saika.
I have to get to him,
or he'll-- he'll be--
[Varona] What happened
to uncontrollable urge?
Where is it?
Perhaps it fade away.
Why have I come here?
What am I doing in city?
Gotta pee something fierce.
What?
[gasp]
What the hell?
Oh!
What's going on, man?
What the heck was that?
I knew she'd take the bait.
-Whoa!
-Huh?
[all scream]
[people exclaiming]
Oh, man. What the hell?
That hurt!
[Walker whimpering]
Yo, Walker, you okay?
What's wrong with you, man?
Say something.
It's here!
My destiny is calling me!
Huh?
Did you see that mysterious
lady in the glasses?
She was all shooting wires
out of her hands!
Then, she took off
out the window
like a superhero!
Now, she's flying over the city
fighting a big, black glob!
The stars have aligned!
She's a teeny-tiny bit
older than I'd hoped for,
but what the hell!
At last, a 2D heroine
has come into my life
and blown the door of my mind
right off its hinges!
[laughing]
Whoo-hoo! All I need's a kiss
from my little sister,
and my power will awaken!
The lady in yellow
will only be in our world
for a little while longer!
Soon, she'll revert
back to her 2D form
and return to the pages
of her manga!
He finally lost it.
-I know it. I can feel it!
-Hey, Celty.
You have anything to do with--
[Walker laughing]
-Hurry back to your manga!
-Oh.
[Mika] Hey, I think
Celty just left.
Huh? What? I didn't
even see her bail.
She followed that lady
right out the window.
That black, smoky thing
is Celty.
Huh?
[Emilia]
Look at this mess!
Okay, you guys,
what in the name
of all that is holy
happened in here?
[crash ]
-Hmm?
-What the--
Huh?
Uh, of course
I think we should--
[horse neighing]
[laughing]
[galloping, neighing]
Wee! Ha-ha!
Here we go again!
What the hell's
going on tonight?
This is nuts.
[neighing]
[murmuring]
[Varona]
Why did I take this job?
I do not know answer.
What would Sloan say
if were here?
There is no one by side now.
[female newscaster]
We have an update
on the explosion
that rocked
Toshima Ward tonight,
where a squad car
suddenly exploded
outside South Ikebukuro
Precinct.
Dozens of officers from the MPD
are combing the city.
However, they still don't have
any leads on the suspect.
[Varona]
Now, I am truly alone.
[boy]
Yo, look who we got here!
It's him!
You're Shizuo Heiwajima,
aren't you? Are you for real?
What're you always dressing
like a bartender for?
Because if you think
you look cool like that,
you don't!
[Shizuo]
I was hoping
if I walked around
long enough,
I'd either run into Izaya
or some of them sword-zombies.
-Oh, well.
-[boy] What'd you say?
You're talking to yourself
like some crazy-ass hobo!
-Beat it.
-Beat it?
What's that? Like, a dance?
Is that what you did
back when you were a kid
a hundred years ago?
You don't look
like the strongest
dude in Ikebukuro.
Uh-oh!
I think he's scared!
He looks like he's gonna
shit his bartender pants!
You gonna tell us why you
look like a bartender?
Huh?
-[boy laughs]
-[growls]
Say something, dumb-ass!
Whoa!
[Shizuo]
Well? You happy now?
S-Sorry, sir!
W-We're cool!
Yeah, we didn't mean anything!
We're sorry!
-Me, too!
-Huh?
Hey! Your bike!
[gasp]
You can have it.
Just don't kill me!
Hmm. I don't want
your jacked-up bike.
[man] Someone busted all
the security cameras here.
I doubt it has anything
to do with the attack,
since it happened
a while ago.
Well, let's check it anyway.
I remember how bad
this city was--
all the fighting.
You mean the color gangs?
Yeah.
Must've been something.
I bet you saw some crazy
stuff, huh, Kuzuhara?
Yeah, I guess.
Around two years ago,
things quieted down.
I get the feeling it's not
going to stay that way.
Kick-ass hideout
you got here.
Yeah, this place has
a lot of potential.
It's a little grimy.
I wouldn't bring a chick
here, but hey, it works.
[people murmuring]
[grunting]
[chuckling]
Ha-ha!
[groan]
[gang member]
Yeah!
You think I'm all talk
and no action?
That I'm a pussy
that lets my crew do
my fighting for me, huh?
Huh? [laughing]
You think playing hero
and coming at me all furious
is enough to take me out?
A pussy like you?
Shut up!
Pop quiz time, you asshole.
[grunting]
There's a time limit
on this one.
Do you know what'll happen
to your bitch-ass crew
if you don't let me kill you?
No! It's cool!
Don't worry about us, Chief!
Just get out of here
while you can!
Oh, sweet!
Another hero!
It's two-for-one day.
What are the odds?
Stop it!
[chuckle]
Time's up.
The answer is:
they're gonna die either way!
-[laughing]
-Kill me if you want.
They've got nothing
to do with this.
What are you talking about?
They got yellow bandanas on,
don't they?
I mean, if I see an enemy,
I gotta take 'em out.
And since you're
the Yellow Scarves
and I'm a Dollar--
[chuckle]
You're in the Dollars?
No way.
You know it. If I don't put
you guys out of commission,
how am I gonna face my boss?
After all, it's what
Mr. Ryugamine wants!
[gasp]
[laughing]
What the hell did you say?
Huh? Mikado Ryugamine?
Trippy name, ain't it?
He's the boss, though.
What do you know
about Mikado?
Let's have it! What are
you gonna do with him?
Pop quiz, part two.
There's a reason
I ain't telling you shit,
and it's not because
you're an asshole.
What is the reason?
The answer is: you're gonna die,
so you can't do anything
about it anyway!
[Chikage]
Hey, dumb-ass!
Don't go butting in
on another guy's fight.
[Izumii]
You bastard.
Move and your boy's eyeball's
gonna be airborne.
-[boy whimpering]
-[Izumii] What are you, nuts?
Not as much as you are, bruh.
[thinking]
He might be super-strong,
but he can't take
all these guys on.
[Chikage] I swear,
You Dollars dicks
are as hard as hell
to figure out.
It blows my mind
that one gang
could have scumbags
like you in it
and have a guy
like Kadota, too.
You know Kadota?
Yep. Surprised you know him.
Huh. He don't seem
like the kind of guy
that likes hanging out
with the rats.
[grunt] You can have
his eye if you want.
[gang member]
Izumii!
You'll pay for it
with your life!
So, I can have his eye,
but I gotta die for it?
Man, that's
the shittiest deal ever.
[Izumii] You think
I was gonna let you
walk out of here,
you asshole?
-[whimpering]
-Like I said, you're nuts.
So am I for picking
a fight up here.
We're both stupid
to start a brawl
with security cameras
watching.
I bet the cops are
on their way right now.
You think we'd be
up here doing this
if we didn't bust
the cameras first?
Hell, even if
we left them alone,
I could still beat
the piss out of you
and split before
the cops show.
Oh, yeah?
Where you going, bruh?
You scared?
There's nowhere to run,
so you might as--
Kick his ass!
[alarm rings]
[murmuring]
[chuckling]
[Izumii]
Son of a bitch!
You-- You think
you got me down?
[indistinct chatter]
You okay?
The cops will be here
any second!
Come on, man, we gotta bail!
Shit!
I won't forget this, you--
Aah!
Izumii!
Sorry about this.
Hey!
It would be faster
if you ride with me.
We can settle things up later.
Y'all might wanna
get going now.
-But, Chief?
-What do you think you're--
-[yelps]
-[boy] Where are you going?
Uh-- Wh--
[screaming]
Aah!
Ah. Ha-ha-ha!
[Masaomi]
Oh, yeah? Thank God.
No, I'm good for now.
Sit tight. I'll call you
in a little while.
Yeah.
[phone beeps]
[Chikage]
Your guys all safe?
Yeah, just barely.
-So?
-What?
I might not look it,
but I'm a good listener.
At least that's what all
my honeys keep telling me.
It's running on instinct.
Whatever consciousness
it had is gone.
It seems it's lost all sanity
in this form as well.
[thinking]
How can I be sure
I will fight as before?
Life in peace of city
does nothing but dull edge.
Sloan tell me this.
How dare you question
my skill as fighter!
Are you mocking me?
I deny it,
but, in back of mind,
I knew truth.
I did not mind
to be that way.
Then, I meet man I try to kill
but could not in end.
He make me question values,
lose sense of purpose.
Shizuo Heiwajima.
In days I spend
as trainee under Shizuo,
I feel different kind of bliss
I never feel before.
Nothing like bliss
of battle in past.
I become aware of world
I have never known before.
Then, Shizuo taken away.
That was when
I receive new offer.
[vehicle beeping]
It was during attack
I have old feeling back again.
[people murmuring]
Longing for pursuit
of power return.
I was almost convinced
this world was world
I belong in.
Hey!
[gasp]
Varona. It's you, isn't it?
[snarling]
Even though
you're a monster,
your goals are not
destruction and hate.
You have
more important things
to pursue, don't you?
I'm surprised
to be saying this,
but I'm feeling
rather jealous.
Uh, I guess she can
be stubborn, huh?
[Varona]
Shadow is most likely
Headless Rider.
Why Kasane Kujiragi target it?
Now I think of it,
job did not come
from Jinnai Yodogiri.
Offer come from Kasane.
She give job
to fight monster.
What would Sloan say
if were here?
And what is wrong with man?
Eyes are red.
Perhaps infected with virus.
It possible Headless Rider
chasing man.
Why? Are they enemies?
Why would it hate him?
Or...
perhaps it in love with man.
What is love?
I have never loved anyone.
It possible I do not
even love self.
I am aware of concept,
but am unsure if love
is required in life.
It's not like air or food.
Whatever case may be,
this emotion called love
is not same as emotion
I could feel during daily life
in peace of city.
Is not same as feeling
during battle.
I can no longer feel
that way again.
Cover has been compromised.
I have been seen by Shizuo.
By Shizuo?
I see now
what this loneliness,
this desolation,
this sense of loss really is.
I did not realize
how afraid I was
to lose daily life in city.
Now, I do.
Nothing ever happen here.
Is true.
But, here, I find
what it mean to live
and satisfaction that come
from peaceful existence.
Is too late to turn back now.
There is nothing I can do.
I no longer have peaceful
daily life to return to.
I am alone.
Goddamn it.
Hmm?
-[neighing]
-Is that Celty?
-[men whimpering]
-[neighing]
Hmm.
Aren't you supposed
to be, uh, you know,
Celty's bike?
Where is she?
You want me to get on you?
Uh, I've never rode
a horse before.
[nickering]
[neighing]
Sorry, I never learned how
to ride a motorbike, either.
What do you want?
Huh? Oh, this thing?
Yeah, some punk-ass kid
gave it to me tonight.
[gasp]
[bike bell rings]
Man, you're something else,
aren't you?
Yeah, sure, this'll work.
I can ride one no swea--
Let me guess.
Something happened
to Celty, didn't it?
[bike bell ringing]
All right.
Let's get going, then!
[gasp]
How's it going?
We haven't met before, I think.
No, we haven't.
Thought so.
Nice to meet you.
I'm Saki.
Uh...
[thinking]
Something ain't right here.
It's no coincidence
that everything's coming
to a head like this.
And there's only one guy
I know who'd be behind it.
Izaya!
♪ [singing in Japanese]
[Chikage] Okay, now,
it's getting complicated.
We've got all these stories
about all these people
crisscrossing
all over the place
like a frickin' spiderweb.
I'm getting in
on the action, too,
'cause, hey, it's what I do.
Next time: In For a Penny,
In For a Pound.