["Day You Laugh"
by Toyonaga Toshiyuki]
♪ ♪
[man singing in Japanese]
‐ [gasps]
[thud]
‐ Huh?
‐ What happened to him?
‐ No way!
‐ For now, all I want from you
is one email addy.
Give me that,
and I'll leave you alone.
‐ I need to see you
right now,
and call the others.
I want to see them, too.
‐ And the Dullahan's head, too.
I'll take 'em all.
Name your price.
Can you deliver the goods,
Mr. Yodogiri?
[man singing in Japanese]
♪ ♪
ERIKA: That night,
news of the hit‐and‐run
spread like wildfire
across Ikebukuro.
Everyone was affected by it.
I guess that just shows you
how important
Dotachin was to folks,
doesn't it?
[cheering]
Well, not to everyone.
A few people were stoked
when they found out.
You can ignore
those dirtbags.
Everyone knew about it
by the time the news
got to these two.
‐ Our Kyohei's in a coma?
‐ Yes.
He was involved
in a hit‐and‐run.
‐ You're kidding.
So what do the doctors say?
Will he make it?
‐ They don't know yet.
They're waiting to see
if he'll regain consciousness.
‐ I see.
‐ I want to go visit him,
but I doubt the hospital
is going to let me
through the front door.
‐ I'm really worried.
‐ He'll pull through it.
He's a tough cookie.
‐ It's not him.
You're the one
I'm worried about, Celty.
Even if Kyohei comes to,
he's going to be in the hospital
for a while.
What if, I don't know, something
flares up in the Dollars
while he's out of commission?
Knowing you, you'd try
to help, wouldn't you?
‐ Don't worry.
Whether he's around or not,
I doubt anything's
gonna go that wrong.
It's not like he's their
leader or anything.
‐ I don't know.
It's like he and Shizuo
keep people in line.
Shizuo's the Dollars' muscle,
and Kyohei's the conscience,
dealing with external threats
and internal ones.
Kyohei's always hated it
when people called him
the face of the Dollars,
but now that it's
gotten so big,
if some kind of
conflict comes up
he's the guy everyone
turns to for advice.
‐ Yeah, I guess you have
a point there.
‐ [groaning]
It'll be fine.
No matter what happens
with the Dollars,
the important thing is you do
what you think is right.
In the end, I don't care
if you piss off
every person on Earth.
I'll always be on your side.
‐ Don't worry about me.
The last thing I want to do
is screw up so bad
everyone's after me.
I'll keep tabs
on Kyohei's condition.
If anything changes,
I'll let you know ASAP.
‐ Thanks.
‐ I'll go fix you
something to eat.
[phone chimes]
ERIKA: In another part of town,
these guys were
having a meeting.
‐ I hope you're not looking
for an interview.
If you are, you should have
made an appointment.
‐ That's not what I'm here,
Mr. Shiki.
I hate to bother you
with personal stuff but‐‐
‐ You're not bothering anybody.
I'm happy to help if I can.
‐ Thanks.
‐ Seeing as how you want
to talk to me,
whatever you problem you've got
must be the serious kind.
Am I right?
‐ Yeah, it is sort of.
I‐I need your help
with a family matter.
ERIKA: So he told him his story,
about his missing daughter,
about getting texts from her
and not knowing where she was,
and about how
he thought the Dollars
might have something
to do with it.
‐ I get where
you're coming from.
I bet you're worried sick.
‐ Do you know anything
about the Dollars?
I've been asking everyone,
but no one's talking.
‐ I don't know
what to tell you.
You think they're a color gang,
but they're not.
Just a bunch of office workers,
students and squares
who want to belong
to something,
not the kind of thing
my outfit keeps tabs on.
Know what I'm saying?
‐ Yeah, yeah,
I guess you guys wouldn't.
But I heard that recently
there's shady things going on
inside the Dollars.
‐ Yeah, well,
it's a big group of people.
It's a cinch there'd be
a few bad eggs.
You can't expect them
to stay in line,
'cause they don't got a boss.
‐ Yeah, I know,
but every time I ask someone
who's a Dollar about it,
they won't talk to me.
I keep hitting one dead end
after another.
If I could figure out
how to crack their ranks,
I'd find some answers,
but I'm not hip to the ways
of the underworld.
‐ Oh, I get it.
So here you are
chatting with a gangster,
'cause you think
since I'm a gangster
I might be able
to get you in with them.
‐ Yeah, I guess.
‐ I thought so.
I'm gonna hook you up
with a guy in my outfit
who's dialed in
to that stuff.
‐ Oh, that's great.
Thank you.
I don't know how I'm gonna pay
you back for this though.
‐ The name of this game
is we scratch your back,
you scratch ours.
That's how you pay us back.
‐ Oh, sure.
‐ Do us a favor sometime.
Like if something comes up
and we can use your talents,
you help us out
and we'll be square.
‐ Thank you.
That sounds fair.
‐ Then let's get
the ball rolling.
I'll call my guy
and set up a meeting.
You know what people call him?
Red Ogre.
Yeah, but these days
his horns and fangs
ain't as sharp
as they used to be.
‐ Yeah, I'm okay
with talking to him.
I'm in the middle
of something now,
so send him
to the bar later.
Sorry about that.
So this Mikado Ryugamine kid,
you sure he's the one
who started up the Dollars?
‐ As sure as I can be,
but I'm shocked
to say the least.
To think their founder's
from my alma mater.
‐ Heh. Don't give me
the clueless act, info‐broker.
I bet you homed in on this kid
'cause you knew exactly
who he was.
‐ If I said yes,
would it make any difference?
We both know more
than we're letting on,
don't we, Mr. Akabayashi?
You knew he was the leader
all along, too.
‐ Oh, you think?
Either way,
I kind of figure this info
was something you'd want
to keep to yourself.
‐ Why would I do that?
‐ If you kept it a secret,
it might be worth more later on,
but if you played that angle
and someone like me found out,
that would be bad.
‐ I wouldn't dream of it.
And honestly,
I'm just not that clever.
You'd have to be to keep
secrets from the Awakusu.
‐ Cut the crap.
I doubt you'd be
in business this long
unless you had a trick or two
up your sleeve.
The Dollars have gotten so big,
they're like a goddamn city now.
It's only a matter of time
before it goes up in smoke.
‐ Oh, you think so?
Why's that?
‐ 'Cause there's a firebug
who wants to watch it burn,
but there might be others
starting fires, too.
And if he's not careful,
he just might get caught
in someone else's fire.
ERIKA: While that was happening,
Dotachin was having
a second operation.
Things looked beyond serious
for him.
But all we could do was sit
and wait for it to be over.
You didn't get any sleep
last night.
Go home, get some rest,
and I'll call you
when he comes out.
‐ No, he's helped me so many
times, so I'll manage.
But how are you doing?
You didn't get
much sleep either.
‐ Hmm.
I'm still hanging in there.
I hope they are, too.
If it wasn't for Dotachin,
none of us would be
on the straight and narrow,
especially me.
‐ Oh.
‐ As long as I've known him,
he's never been the type
to turn his back
on someone in trouble.
He's the kind
of nice guy archetype
you don't see much
even in manga.
Oh, and look at how crowded
this waiting room is,
and you'll get a sense
of how many people he's helped.
He can't have visitors yet,
but they keep on coming.
What are they thinking?
He's in surgery
for Christ's sake.
Oh, well, what you gonna do?
‐ So, uh, where's Walker and‐‐
sorry, I forget
the driver guy's name?
‐ Doing what they do.
See, Dotachin's more
than a friend to us.
He's also our brakeman.
‐ Brakeman?
‐ Crap, it's starting to rain.
‐ Told you.
‐ Goddamn, this is good.
‐ Huh? Can I try?
Come on, give me a bite.
‐ Huh?
[tires squeal]
‐ What the hell?
‐ You asshole!
‐ You son of a bitch!
‐ Yo, you trying to kill us
or what?
‐ Kushi High never changes.
You're supposed to be
on your summer break.
Do you ever take
your uniforms off?
‐ Oh, you got a problem
with that, wise‐ass?
‐ You wanna die or something?
‐ Huh, what's up,
you little dick fart?
[overlapping chatter]
‐ No way, Togusa?
all: Huh?
‐ Hey.
‐ 'Sup?
Yo, show some respect.
He used to go to our school.
‐ Oh, shit.
We had no idea.
Sorry.
both: Sorry, sir.
‐ It's cool.
No harm, no foul.
The reason I'm here
is to apologize
for something I'm gonna do.
‐ Huh?
‐ What are you gonna do?
‐ I'm gonna kill someone
by dragging him behind my van.
You can see how doing that would
ruin Kushi High's rep,
can't you?
ERIKA: It goes without saying
that some people
had a hard time
sitting around waiting.
If I could be out there too,
I would.
Believe me.
‐ I got a problem.
One of my best friends
is heading for trouble.
I want to stop him,
even if I have to kick
his ass to do it.
Thing is,
I can't do it on my own.
I hate dragging you into this,
but I really need your help.
‐ We got your back, chief,
you know that.
‐ Yeah, just tell us
what to do.
‐ Yeah, chief,
we're down for whatever.
‐ Hell yeah.
‐ You're damn straight.
‐ Uh‐huh.
‐ You got it.
‐ Yeah, chief, we're with you.
‐ All the way.
‐ All right, guys, the name
of the person we're going after
is Mikado Ryugamine.
He's the leader of the Dollars.
Yatabe should have
been here by now.
[door opens]
‐ What took you so long?
‐ It's about time.
‐ Um...
‐ Yo, what's wrong, man?
‐ 'Sup, Masaomi?
Short time no see or something.
‐ Walker, how'd you know
we were gonna be here?
‐ Are you kidding?
I just followed your boy here.
I figured if you're bringing
the Yellow Scarves back,
it's a cinch you'd be needing
your right‐hand man.
I'm all crafty like that.
‐ Oh.
Okay then, why are you here?
You wouldn't happen
to be the guy
that ran Kyohei over,
are you?
‐ The reason I'm sitting here
waiting for Dotachin to wake up
is so I can call the boys
and stop them
before they can
do anything drastic.
They're out there right now
looking for the guy who hit him.
‐ They are?
‐ Oh, yeah.
And if they catch the dude
who did it before the cops do,
they'll most definitely
kill the bastard.
‐ [gasps]
‐ Heck, if I found him,
I'd kill him, too.
‐ What is this place?
It looks like there was a fire.
‐ Halfway through building it,
the owners bailed.
Then a while ago,
something went down here
with the yakuza.
And since then,
people avoid it.
‐ I guess this place is as good
a spot to meet as any,
but don't you think it's kind
of far from Ikebukuro?
‐ That's the best part about it.
No one's gonna bother us
way out here.
‐ Yeah, good point.
Well, let's find out
what the Dollars are up to.
‐ Damn, you're fast.
‐ In one day, things have
gotten worse in the city.
I bet it's 'cause of
what happened to Kyohei.
ERIKA: People who post crap
like that should be banned.
Go get 'em, Mikado.
Boy's got skills!
That's the leader
of the Dollars for you.
ERIKA: This right here
is something to worry about.
‐ Come on, Walker, seriously?
Does it look like
I can afford a car?
‐ You got it all wrong,
Masaomi.
I'm not saying you did it,
but what about
someone from your crew?
It's possible one or two
of these fine, upstanding gents
went rogue behind
the boss's back.
You know, it does happen
in manga and real life.
‐ Yeah, I guess.
‐ There's all these rumors
about the Yellow Scarves
getting back together, right?
And online it's like the war
between the Scarves
and the Dollars never died down.
So there's that.
‐ I don't think
anyone here did it.
But if it turns out
I'm wrong...
‐ Then?
‐ Then you do
whatever you have to
to make it right.
‐ [chuckles]
I'm going to look
for the guy now,
but if I find out
it was one of yours,
I'll be back.
It'd be a shame
if Asuna got singed.
‐ Oh.
‐ What the hell?
‐ That guy's a freak.
‐ Right?
‐ Can't believe we let him
walk out after talking shit.
‐ Don't tell me
you guys can't smell that.
‐ What?
[all sniffing]
‐ What the hell is that?
‐ Kerosene.
He had a Molotov on him,
and depending on how things
went down here,
he would have used it.
‐ Hey, you know what?
I totally forgot something.
[all scream]
Masaomi, I don't know
if you heard,
but Shizuo is in big trouble.
For real.
‐ You can't take
that post seriously.
It could just be
someone trolling.
‐ I don't think so.
This member's posts have all
been legit up till now.
So it's a good bet
this one is too.
‐ Don't tell me you can remember
every single post
made by every member.
‐ Nah, just the ones
that stick out.
Anyway, this is good.
‐ Huh?
‐ I'm glad Shizuo got arrested
after he quit the Dollars.
Can't have any bad apples.
In a way, I'm glad he's there.
‐ What do you mean?
‐ If Kyohei was still
walking around
and found out about what I'm
trying to do with the Dollars,
he'd stop me for sure.
‐ There's no doubt about it,
Mikado's slipped a cog.
Was he always this twisted
or did he get this way
after we showed up?
Maybe we were drawn to him
because he's broken.
Maybe this is
the best place for us.
Now that they're out of the
picture, what will you do?
‐ About what?
‐ Well, with Kadota
in the hospital
and that Shizuo guy
locked up in jail,
the Dollars will collapse.
They were the ones
people looked up to.
‐ Yeah, you have
a good point there.
If you have an idea,
speak up.
‐ We need someone to take
their place in the Dollars.
The Dollars need a symbol
to represent them, right?
‐ A symbol?
‐ Yeah, someone the whole city
knows by sight
but don't know anything about.
A famous person
who everyone knows
is a member of the Dollars.
There's one person like that.
‐ You mean...
‐ Exactly!
And I have a feeling
they'd be down
with helping us
clean out the Dollars.
Isn't that right,
Headless Rider?
‐ Wait, Celty?
What are you doing here?
Hey, wait, what's going on?
How do you guys
know each other?
I mean, what, are you
friends now or something?
When did that happen?
Come on, Celty, say something.
‐ We ran into each other
a little while ago.
I apologized for what
happened at the warehouse.
I gave her my email
and she gave me hers.
Help me.
No actually, it's Mikado and me.
Right now we both
need your help.
Yeah, see, what happened
to Kadota is a huge issue
for the Dollars.
Without him, we've lost
our most ideal member.
Heck, there's talk
about Dollars going nuts
and causing all kinds
of trouble across the city.
Even Heiwajima's quit us.
So now we need a new symbol
to hold us together.
‐ And you want me
to be that symbol, is that it?
‐ Thank God, you understand.
‐ No, thanks.
The Dollars shouldn't
have a symbol.
That's the whole point of it.
We're not exactly friends.
Acquaintances.
‐ I had no idea.
How come you never told me.
‐ I didn't mean anything by it.
I just wanted to surprise you,
is all.
‐ Well, I guess you got
what you wanted.
So what's up?
‐ I came here because there's
something I wanted to ask you.
‐ Sure.
What is it?
‐ Mikado, what do you want
to do with the Dollars?
‐ I guess I want us to‐‐oh.
[shoes clacking]
[all gasp]
‐ I was hoping
I could join the party,
if that's all right,
Mikado Ryugamine.
ERIKA: Earlier that afternoon,
a lady on the run
was on her way back
to her hiding place.
She was on high alert,
the way she always was.
But...
‐ [gasps]
‐ Long time no see, Namie.
What, you think we weren't
going to find you?
‐ No, I didn't, President.
‐ Oh, come on now. Why don't
you call me, Uncle Seitarou?
That sounds much better,
doesn't it?
‐ [sighs]
You sold out my father
and the others
for the sake of the company,
so don't talk to me like family.
‐ Whoa, we can hash
that out later.
How 'bout we get out
of the rain, first?
‐ Why?
Afraid someone might see us?
‐ Exactly.
It would be in your best
interest to come quietly.
‐ Kasane Kujiragi.
‐ I'm surprised and honored
that you know my name.
‐ If you're Jinnai Yodogiri's
secretary,
why are you with my uncle?
[groans]
You look so calm,
considering the situation.
Do you have ice water
for blood?
‐ You don't really expect me
to answer that.
[whirring]
‐ [screams]
‐ I can put her to sleep,
if you want me to.
Just say the word.
‐ No, don't bother.
If you put her out now,
it's not going
to help any of us
when we bring her dear
little Seiji around.
‐ Seiji?
‐ Just to warn you,
we might have to hurt him
a little bit,
but I think you'll agree
that's the best way
to make sure you cooperate.
‐ If you lay a finger
on Seiji, you'll regret it.
I swear,
I'll peel your skin off
with a molding plane,
dissolve you both
in a vat of acid.
I'll take a grater
and scrape at you...
ERIKA: And so on a rainy day,
Namie Yagiri disappeared again.
‐ [screams]
KANRA: Good evening, everyone.
Kanra's back!
Meow!
SHARO: Yo.
CHROME: Good evening.
KANRA: Sharo, you should change
your name to Meowru.
Cute!
SHARO: No.
And eww.
CHROME: I'm with Sharo
on this one.
KANRA: Oh, I see how it is.
Two big brutes ganging up
on a helpless girl.
And you call yourselves men.
CHROME: Yes, well, we don't know
if you're really a girl,
now do we?
KANRA: Hmm, then I'll
tell you something
that's going to make you
shiver in fear like little boys.
SHARO: I'm shaking already.
KANRA: A biker gang might
go to war with a color gang
in Ikebukuro.
SHARO: Wait, where did
you hear this?
KANRA: You've heard about
the Yellow Scarves
getting back together, right?
I think they're doing it
so they can start a war
with the Dollars.
Meow!
Kadota's hit‐and‐run
was them saying,
"Come at me!"
Meow.
But have you heard the other
rumor floating around?
SHARO: Hold on, that crap
about the Yellow Scarves,
that's for real?
CHROME: So what's
this other rumor?
KANRA:
You know the Dragon Zombies?
CHROME: Sure,
they're a biker gang.
KANRA: Bingo!
Your prize for correctly
answering is one meow, Chrome.
Meow.
CHROME: Keep it.
KANRA: Anyway, the rumor is
people wearing
Dragon Zombie jackets
were seen close to where
Kadota got hit by that car.
And there's
another rumor I heard
that says there are
a whole bunch of Dragon Zombies
in the Dollars.
SHARO: Hang on a minute.
Are you saying the Dragon
Zombies took over the Dollars
and tried to kill Kadota?
CHROME: Hi there, Kanra.
I wanted to talk
about something in private.
Uh‐oh, posting blanks is such
a newb thing to do,
and I know you're not.
That said, who are you?
How very interesting.
Someone has access
to my Kanra account
and is pretending to be me.
And going by
their IP address,
it's not one of my sisters.
Well, hope they're having fun.
Who ends a post with "meow"?
Lame.
["Exit" by Revalcy]
[man singing in Japanese]
♪ ♪
SHIKI: People meet other people.
Dots connect and make a line.
Lines connect and become fate.
Fate takes people on a journey,
spinning a story along the way.
Next time, "It Takes a Thief
to Catch a Thief."