["Day You Laugh"
by Toyonaga Toshiyuki]
♪ ♪
[man singing in Japanese]
‐ ♪ Da da da da! ♪
Banzai!
[men shouting]
‐ See, Dotachin's more than
a friend to us.
He's also our brakeman.
‐ Anyway, this is good.
I'm glad Shizuo got arrested
after he quit.
Can't have any bad apples.
‐ Raa‐‐uhh!
AKABAYASHI: I think a nap would
do you a world of good.
Hey, mind if I join the party?
[man singing in Japanese]
♪ ♪
SHIKI: Whether by fate
or by accident,
one thing's for sure:
people can't help
meeting each other.
They meet and part ways
as friends
just to pass each other
later on and come into conflict.
Who knows why that is.
‐ Why don't you call it a day,
Anri?
I'm gonna go home
and take a shower myself.
When he wakes up,
I'll tell him, "Yo,
"if you came to sooner,
you would have seen this angel
in a sexy maid outfit with
glasses and a huge rack," okay?
‐ Okay.
[somber music]
I feel bad calling her,
but I need to talk to someone.
[line ringing]
WOMAN: The person
you're trying to reach
is either out of our
service area or is not‐‐
[somber music continues]
♪ ♪
‐ Hey, there, Maju.
How's my niece doing?
‐ Hmm? Hey, what's up?
‐ Can you believe that shit?
Hit and run on my turf.
Can't wait to catch him.
‐ It's lucky the guy
that got hit didn't die.
Things are gonna start
getting crazy here.
‐ Yeah. I heard
the victim's supposed to be
a big shot in a gang.
‐ Yep. Kyohei Kadota
of the Dollars.
The town's also buzzing about
Shizuo Heiwajima's arrest.
Everyone in Public Safety's
gonna be slammed
till it calms down.
‐ Shizuo Heiwajima.
Is he the guy
who dresses like a bartender?
‐ Yep, that's him‐‐they say
he's involved in the Dollars
and that he's friends with that
Headless Rider thing too.
‐ No way!
Him and that monster are tight?
Ha. The last thing I expected
was for it
to have a social life.
‐ Come on,
don't be so pissed off.
He'll be out in no time.
You'll see.
‐ I do not understand
invocation here.
What reason would I have
to be angry
because Shizuo
have been arrested?
There is no connection
between two things.
‐ Well, at least you knew
what "pissed off" meant.
I'll give ya that.
‐ I do not understand
why Shizuo have been arrested.
This make no sense at all.
‐ The cops always
had their eye on him.
All they needed
was an excuse to jump.
So when that chick
filed that complaint,
they saw their chance, see?
We both know
Shizuo's not the type of guy
to kick someone's ass
for no reason,
especially if it's a chick.
It's either
a big misunderstanding
or maybe‐‐I don't know‐‐
someone's trying to frame him.
‐ If you just wanna
question him,
why does he have to go in?
I'm callin' my lawyer!
‐ Don't worry, boss.
I haven't done anything wrong,
so it's cool.
♪ ♪
‐ To break out of cell would be
like play of child for Shizuo.
Then if he is fugitive from law
I can fight him
and claim
I was defending self later.
But then, cannot pay him back
for coffee in can
or for taking me
to delicious cake shop.
And there is also fact
I am not yet skilled enough
to defeat him.
But why do I do this?
Why do I keep looking for reason
to not fight Shizuo?
‐ Is long time no see,
da, Varona?
‐ Sloan‐‐is you!
[gasps]
So you survive after all.
Why have you not contacted me
until now?
‐ I would have liked to,
but I've been a little busy.
[muffled] They ripped out
ten of my teeth.
And now the Awakusu
assigned me new job
as assistant to broker
of information in city.
‐ I am sorry,
but I am also relieved
that you are still living.
‐ No time for relief.
Keep guard up.
If you know what good,
you will get out of city.
Soon it will become dangerous
here for you.
‐ You make no sense.
Only danger here
is becoming bored with self.
‐ War is to happen here,
and you and I are to be used
as pawns in it.
‐ I welcome challenge.
If anyone should dare
to drag me into plot,
I am more than able
to make them regret decision.
‐ But how can you be sure
you will fight as before?
Life in peace of city does
nothing but dull edge, da?
‐ How dare you question
my skill as fighter.
Are you mocking me?
‐ Now, now, Sloan.
You shouldn't be so mean
to the lady.
Sometimes peace and quiet
is what a body needs.
Perhaps the tranquility
of the city has recharged her
and now she's become
even more dangerous
than she ever was before.
‐ And...you are?
‐ That's right.
We never officially met.
I hired you before, though.
I'm Izaya Orihara, the info
broker of this wonder city.
‐ Izaya Orihara.
Da. I remember.
‐ Really? I hire you for one
job, and you remember me?
[chuckles]
You are a‐‐
[dramatic musical sting]
[grunting]
‐ I have heard rumor
from others on street
you are mortal enemy of Shizuo.
I will now take opportunity
to annihilate you
and return multitude favors
I am owing him.
‐ Well...I didn't know Shizuo
had the charm
to tame a girl like you.
[exhales] Whatever.
It should be amusing to see
whose pawn you become.
And since observing humans
is a hobby of mine,
you've piqued my interest.
I am looking forward to watching
what happens to you next.
Even if you're friends
with a monster like him,
I still like you as a human.
Apparently,
the feeling is not mutual.
Back to work.
‐ Hmm? What do you mean?
I thought we are done for day.
‐ Not quite. I haven't heard
from Namie since it got dark.
I think it's safe to say
they got to her first.
We have to wrap this up
by tomorrow morning.
The sooner we do, the better for
your ex‐comrade here.
With any luck, she can avoid
becoming their pawn.
SHIKI: Izaya Orihara's taunts
filled Varona's heart
with cold poison,
‐ [Izaya chuckles]
SHIKI: Changing it back into
the icy thing it was when she
first arrived in the city.
AKABAYASHI:
You got a problem I'm here,
Mikado?
‐ Huh?
[whimpers]
Crap! He's gonna kill me.
I don't wanna die.
Not yet‐‐I still have
so much to do.
Oh, God!
‐ Ha. Ya passed the test, kid.
A real gangster ain't gonna
shit himself in a staredown.
‐ Huh?
‐ You got a problem, old man?
‐ What's up, bitch?
You got a death wish?
‐ Uhh‐‐ugh!
‐ How'd you do that?
‐ I picked up a few tricks
in my day.
Hell, some folks think
I'm psychic, I move so fast.
[chuckling]
Can you beat that?
What do you think, Transporter?
Am I psychic?
‐ Sorry.
Who are you?
CELTY:
Is it okay to tell him?
‐ Sure, go ahead.
It's what I came here to do.
‐ This is Mr. Akabayashi.
He's with the Awakusus.
‐ The Awakusus?
‐ Hey, you heard of us!
Then I guess
I don't have to tell you
if a guy like me
comes around looking for ya,
it's gotta be serious.
‐ Is it us?
Have we caused you trouble?
‐ Well... let's just say
you have our attention.
Some of the higher‐ups think
we need to take action.
But I'm not into
roughing up civvies.
Kind of a rule with me.
‐ Ohh...
‐ I'm here
to give you a choice.
You can either be our partners
or get stomped.
Take your pick.
[slow jazzy music]
‐ If the Dollars
did your group wrong,
I swear we didn't mean it.
It's just...
all we want
is a place to belong.
‐ Oh. Is that all?
I'm sure there's tons of places
like that
on the right side of the law.
‐ Mm.
‐ Consider this your first
and last warning.
I don't wanna give you
a hard time.
Just letting you know
that folks like me
got ya on the radar now.
‐ I appreciate you
doing that for us.
‐ Mm‐hmm. You got manners, kid.
I like that.
Now I'm gonna leave you
with some advice.
Quit the Dollars now,
and you'll be better off for it.
If your parents find out
you're the leader of a gang,
it'll break their hearts.
This kinda life ain't good
for you or your friends,
especially that girl
you're tight with‐‐
you know,
the one with the glasses.
‐ Anri's got nothing
to do with this!
‐ See, that's what
I'm talkin' about, kid.
You just let me know
how important she is to you.
Now I'll tell you
something about me.
For six months now, I've been
a member of the Dollars.
‐ [gasps]
‐ Crazy, huh?
Just so you know,
I'll be talking about you later
with the rider here.
‐ Any time. And for the record,
Mikado's not stupid.
He won't get on your bad side.
AKABAYASHI: I hope you're right.
CELTY: I know I am.
‐ Well, before I go,
I need a favor
for something Dollar‐related.
Seeing as how I'm a Dollar too,
I'd like to ask you
to help a friend of mine
who's in a jam.
‐ Who?
‐ You're up, Niekawa.
Come on out
and meet the boss man.
CELTY: Niekawa?
‐ Thanks.
I‐‐Uh‐‐
The shy‐looking kid's
the leader?
For real?
‐ Yep. He's about
the closest thing
to a leader the Dollars have.
Sure, he might not look it,
but I think he can help you.
‐ You're Niekawa, the writer
with the "Tokyo Warriors."
‐ Yeah, that's‐‐
[gasps]
It's‐‐it's the Headless Rider!
‐ What are you doing here?
Are you friends
with Mr. Akabayashi?
‐ No, n‐not exactly.
Like he said,
I'm here to get help.
‐ Um... Celty?
Is this guy a friend
of yours too?
‐ No. A while back,
he interviewed me about Shizuo.
That's how we‐‐
‐ Listen!
My daughter's run away,
and I think
she's in the Dollars!
Her name's Haruna.
I need to find her!
Can you help me, please?
Please!
[footsteps]
[dog barks]
‐ [heavy breathing]
[object clatters]
[clattering gets louder]
[tense music]
[clattering]
‐ You goddamn otaku bastard.
It's been a long frickin' time,
hasn't it?
‐ Mr. Izumi?
You look way different.
‐ You gotta be shitting me.
You damn near burn my face off,
and here you are,
calling me mister?
I am so happy,
I got a serious boner right now!
‐ Before we go at it,
I wanna ask you something.
‐ What?
‐ Did you run over Kyohei
last night?
‐ Ha. Oh, right,
that son of a bitch traitor
got mowed down,
and now he's in the hospital!
You asshole!
‐ [grunts]
‐ It's time for
a pop quiz, bitch.
Here's the question.
After I'm done killing you,
whose head am I
gonna smash next?
Here's your only hint:
He's at the hospital
lying in a coma!
[shrill screaming]
Do you always carry
that shit around with you?
‐ Don't you wish people
were color‐coded, like in manga?
If it was like that,
I'd be wearing red,
'cause fire's sort of my thing.
Wait.
Now that I think about it,
you couldn't have been
the one who hit Kyohei.
'Cause if it was you, you would
have made sure he was dead.
‐ You know it.
And I would have drove his ass
up into the mountains
and buried him.
‐ Yeah, thought so.
I shoulda known
you didn't do it.
Oh, by the way,
if you're serious about
paying Kyohei a visit,
Mr. Molotov's
got other plans for you.
‐ Ha! Bring it on, dick!
You already got me once.
It won't happen again!
‐ That line woulda been perfect
if you said something like,
"First I kill your fantasy,
then you!"
‐ Aaaaahhhh!
[classical tune ringtone]
Hello. I was just about
to call you.
‐ Mm...
‐ Yes, sir. I understand.
Sure. I'm on my way.
[beep]
You lucked out tonight,
dickwad!
I'm gonna let you live
another day or two‐‐
you and that Kadota prick!
[huffs]
Hmph!
‐ Huh?
[grunts]
This walking around sucks.
I'm out in the open now,
and if I'm not careful
I could get ambushed again.
I gotta find a place to hide.
Wait. This is awesome!
I get to have a hideout now!
[lightly suspenseful music]
♪ ♪
‐ [gasps]
SHIKI: Seeing the name
Haruna Niekawa again
filled her with
a nameless dread.
Dragging her friends
into something horrible
was the one thing
that scared her the most.
‐ Sorry to call you
out here like this,
but I wanted you to know what's
going on with me right now.
‐ No need to apologize.
I've been meaning
to catch up with you.
‐ Don't think I'm weird,
but talking to you
makes me feel like
I'm in a dream.
It doesn't feel real at all,
like I'm walking around
inside of a movie or something.
‐ You can still
tell the difference
between reality and fiction,
though, right?
‐ I'm not sure
I get what you're saying.
‐ Anri was talking about you
a while ago.
She's worried.
She said you seem
a little too cheerful lately.
‐ Yeah. I guess in a way
I have been.
But I can't help it.
It's fun to be alive.
I know what I wanna do now,
and it feels great
to finally have a purpose.
All my life I was just
going with the flow,
which was fine, I guess...
but I can't go on doing that.
‐ Is that why you're trying
to clean up the Dollars?
‐ You know about that?
It's really
not that big a deal.
I want the Dollars to be perfect
like how it used to be.
That's all I'm trying to do.
‐ But using violence
to kick out the so‐called
troublemakers is wrong.
You can't get rid of all of
them‐‐don't you know that?
Violence never solves anything.
‐ I know it's wrong, Celty,
but I'm doing it
for all the right reasons.
See? It's the same as why
I founded the Dollars.
And that's something
society frowns on too.
‐ Have you heard the rumor
going around
about the Yellow Scarves?
[neon buzzing]
‐ Yeah. I heard.
He's getting the surviving
members back together.
‐ Then you know Masaomi's
gearing up to come after you.
‐ It's better for everyone
you forget I know about that.
And about how me and Masaomi
are leading these gangs and all.
And I'm pretty sure
you know about Anri too.
You know everything.
But please don't tell her
any of this.
See, Anri and I made a promise
a while ago
that when us three
were back together again
we'd talk about
everything that's happened.
‐ But when the Yellow Scarves
come after the Dollars,
and they will,
what are you gonna do?
‐ We're gonna fight, of course.
As a matter of fact,
I sent Alba
and the rest of the guys
to attack
the Yellow Scarves today.
[train wheels rattling]
AOBA: Here we go.
We're about to find out.
how loyal this guy is
to Masaomi Kida.
‐ Tailing them to their hideout
would be easier
than beating the info
out of him.
‐ I don't care if he doesn't
give it up to us.
We need a declaration of war,
and this guy fits the bill.
‐ You did what?
That's insane!
You're insane!
‐ You're overreacting a bit,
Celty.
I'm perfectly sane.
‐ No, you're not!
Why are you doing this?
Is it because you think the
Scarves are being manipulated
like before?
Well, guess what.
You're the one
being manipulated.
Can't you see Aoba's using you?
How can you trust him?
‐ You got it all wrong.
This isn't about trust.
We have an agreement
between us.
He can use me,
and I can use him.
That's all it is.
Don't take this
the wrong way, Celty,
but you have no idea
how strong the bond is
between Masaomi, Anri, and me.
‐ Don't even give me
that high and mighty crap!
‐ The threads that tie me and
Masaomi together got so twisted
we can't untangle them anymore.
So instead...
the only thing to do is burn 'em
and start all over from scratch.
‐ He's serious about this.
MIKADO: I don't know why
Aoba's pushing
for you to be
the Dollar symbol.
But if you don't want to do it,
that's totally fine.
Whatever you end up
deciding, though,
I'd appreciate it if
you ignored what we're doing.
‐ Shut your mouth
and come with us!
Unless you wanna
get your legs broke.
‐ What the hell are they doing?
They're supposed to follow us.
BOTH: Huh?
[overlapping chatter]
‐ I guess the chief
saw this one coming.
AOBA: Oh, shit.
Come on, wake up!
We got trouble!
‐ [groans]
‐ They got away, huh?
Oh, well, it's not a big deal.
Did any of our guys get hurt?
Crap.
Naw, just be careful.
‐ So they made a move on us
after all.
That Aoba guy
has got some balls.
‐ No. Mikado might have
ordered it.
‐ No way! Then I guess Mikado
don't know you're our boss.
That wouldn't have happened
if he did.
‐ Even if he knows about me,
he's comin' for us.
I mean, it's only fair.
I know he's their boss,
and I'm still going after
the Dollars.
‐ Mmm.
‐ I'm coming, Mikado.
You're stuck in the middle of
something you can't get out of.
I get what that's like,
but I'll dig to the rotten
heart of it to get you out.
Even if I have to ask
that bastard for help.
JINNAI: Do we know where
Izaya Orihara is yet?
I'm beginning to get concerned.
‐ I'm sorry about that, sir.
Unfortunately,
we lost track of him yesterday
after we made contact
with Namie Yagiri.
‐ Mm. Well, we'll catch him
eventually.
It's about time we put Shijima
to work for us,
wouldn't you say?
[cell phone rings]
Why is someone calling me
instead of you?
IZAYA: Mr. Jinnai Yodogiri?
It's been a while.
‐ Who is this?
‐ Oh. Are you not
the same Mr. Yodogiri
who stabbed me before?
I'm so sorry.
Allow me to introduce myself
again.
I'm Izaya Orihara,
just your everyday info broker.
‐ Well, well,
this is a surprise.
I was just talking about you,
you know.
IZAYA: Right.
Let me get to the point.
Where is Namie Yagiri?
I did some snooping around
Yagiri Pharmaceuticals
and couldn't find
anything useful.
I was wondering
if she was with you.
‐ You have me at a loss.
You see,
whether she is or isn't,
I'm not obligated
to tell you anything.
IZAYA: Hmm. True. You aren't.
Then how 'bout this?
You sound stressed.
I think a nap would do you
a world of good.
‐ What do you mean, na‐‐
[brakes screech]
[thud]
[engine turns]
[line rings]
MAN: Hello.
Is something wrong?
‐ Yodogiri number eight
has been injured.
You're going to have to take his
place, number five.
YODOGIRI NINE: Of course.
Where should I meet‐‐
[crash]
[tires screech]
[beep]
[ringing]
IZAYA: Hello, Ms. Kujiragi.
It seems your boss doesn't wanna
tell me where Namie is.
Would you please tell me?
That is, if you don't mind.
‐ I'm so sorry
to disappoint you.
I'm not authorized to give out
that kind of information.
IZAYA: That's not true.
You don't need anyone's
authorization,
because everyone
answers to you.
After all, you are the leader
of the group
called Jinnai Yodogiri.
KUJIRAGI: And who told you this?
‐ As a matter of fact,
no one told me,
but after looking at it
from all the angles,
that's the conclusion I came to.
As for the name Kujiragi,
I'm thinking
it's not your real name.
I bet you killed the real
Kujiragi and stole her identity.
KUJIRAGI:
I didn't steal anything.
It was a mutual transaction.
‐ Well, either way,
I don't know your real name,
and that just won't do.
I tried to expose
everything around you,
and that's why those poor
old decoys had to go.
I hope you understand.
On a different topic,
you hijacked my Kanra chat name,
didn't you?
Was ending your post with "meow"
your way of taunting me?
KUJIRAGI: I thought it was cute.
‐ [sighs]
Right. So are you going to
tell me where Namie is?
She's a proud woman,
but unfortunately,
she hates my guts.
When she finds out I saved her,
the look on her face
will be epic.
‐ That doesn't sound
very honorable.
‐ Well, that's funny,
coming from a woman
who does everything
from human trafficking
to monster trafficking.
Know what I find ironic?
Saika‐‐the blade you sold
to Shingen Kishitani.
It's being used against you now.
Thoughts?
KUJIRAGI: There's a reason why
I let something so valuable
go so easily.
Besides slashing humans
to create new offspring,
Saika has another way
to expand her reach.
I like to call it replication.
‐ Huh?
‐ Simply put,
if you break Saika's blade,
you can make new swords
from the pieces.
[thudding, clatter over phone]
[dark string music]
SLOAN: Mother,
I have captured Izaya.
‐ Would you please bring him
to number 12's office?
I'd like to ask him
some questions
about the Dullahan's head.
‐ Da, Mother.
‐ Thank you very much,
Mr. Izaya Orihara.
You destroyed the group
called Jinnai Yodogiri.
I'll be forever grateful
for that.
[eerie music]
Thank you for my freedom.
[Cóiste‐Bodhar neighs]
CELTY: I've been alive
for centuries,
and I can't even talk sense
into one boy.
‐ Oh, Celty, you're home!
We were getting worried
about you.
‐ Hi, Emilia.
I had a tough day and‐‐
What's with all the food?
‐ We're having ourselves
a dinner party tonight!
And we're gonna have tons of fun
with tons of yummy food
and tons of yummy people
and more food!
Guess who's in time
for din‐dins!
[eerie music continues]
♪ ♪
Now, this is what I call...
‐ It's nice to meet you.
‐ Who the‐‐
[engine whirs]
‐ Welcome home, Celty.
I missed you so much today.
You'd think having all these
people hanging out
would help kill the loneliness,
but they don't.
You're the only one
who can do that.
‐ Thank you, you're sweet.
What's going on?
Why is everyone
in our apartment?
‐ Yeah, funny story...
SHIKI: Whether by fate
or by design,
these people
were brought together here
in this... apartment.
[upbeat music]
♪ ♪