♪ [man singing in Japanese]
I like a good cat fight
as much as the next guy.
[Izaya] I think a nap would
do you a world of good.
[Kine]
When Mikage hauled off
and gave you that kick,
I could totally see you
grit your teeth.
Get ready, because
this nobody's come back
to cut the life out of you!
♪ [singing continues]
[Shingen, narrating]
So let's talk about women.
Elegant ones, hookers,
young ones, yaoi fan girls...
Women are women.
This is a story
about all kinds of women--
like this one, for example.
-Now what?
-Oh, he's always late.
He'll be here soon.
A young woman with a heart
bursting with secrets.
Hi, Erika.
[chuckle] Hi, Anri.
I didn't know
you were coming.
Guess what. The doc said
Dotachin might wake up today.
I really hope he does.
-I'm sorry.
-For what?
Why are you apologizing
out of the blue like that?
Because I'm not here
to see Kyohei today.
I came to talk to you
about something,
and I--I don't know
who else I can
talk to about it.
Oh, is that all?
That's not a big deal.
Whatever you want
to talk about,
jump in my lap
and lay it on me.
It's not that simple.
I want you to know
everything about me.
Huh! No way!
Are you going yuri on me?
Not that I have
a problem with it.
It could be cool with you.
Holy baloney!
You're going to ask me
to have a four-way with you,
Mika-bu, and Masaomi?
Is that what this is about?
Oh, my God, no.
It's not even like that.
Well, look who it is.
I haven't seen you ladies
in forever.
I heard your boy Kadota
was in an accident,
so I came by to see
how he's doing.
What room is he in?
You are?
Oh, come on.
You don't remember me?
That breaks my heart.
On second thought,
last time you saw me,
I was all bandaged up
like a friggin' mummy.
I guess it's better
you don't remember.
[gasp]
I'm Chikage Rokujo.
What's up? You know,
if you ladies want,
you can call me Rocchi.
You're the guy from Toramaru.
Hate to break it
to you, Rocchi,
but the hospital's
only letting family in
to see him for now,
and they're being
super-strict.
The good news is,
he got out of surgery okay,
but he's still unconscious.
Ah. That's good to hear.
But you know what?
It was even better hearing how
you called me Rocchi just now.
Can I get your info?
Yeah, sure.
Sweet. Whoa. Erika Karasawa.
Pretty cool name
you got there.
And, uh, can I get your name,
too, while I'm at it?
Oh. Uh, my name's
Anri Sonohara.
Not so fast, buster.
She's off limits.
She's already got a load
of potential boyfriends
to sort through.
Oh, yeah? If it's cool, can I
throw my hat in the ring, too?
Uh...
[grumbling]
Hey, I don't know too much
about what happened to Kadota.
Like, what kind
of asshole would want
to run him down anyway?
Don't know. The cops are
still out looking for him.
Oh. It was a hit and run.
Mm-hmm. Yeah.
That sucks.
Well, I'd better
get going now.
Could you do me a favor?
Shoot me a text
when he wakes up.
-Okay.
-Me and the honeys are
going to Nanjatown.
And as soon as I
can ditch them,
I'm going to prowl around
Bukuro like a boss.
Excuse me, mister. You're
not ditching anyone, got that?
-You're so--
-[elevator door closes]
Hey, Rocchi,
what was up with that
funny look back there?
You're thinking bad boy
thoughts, aren't you?
[thinking] I'm going to get
my revenge on Ikebukuro,
but the first
order of business
is to find the guy
that tried to off Kadota.
[chuckling]
Well, you can't
have it all.
Oh, well. It's a bust.
Ms. Kujiragi never showed.
Either she's being
very cautious,
or maybe she knows
we've been waiting
for her.
Well, if you're right,
isn't it dangerous
for us to be here?
Considering Saika's powers,
it's dangerous
no matter where we are.
It's 9.
Okay. So?
The hospital opens
at 9. Get going.
I'm sorry. Are you
saying I should go?
Oh, please. I don't
need a hospital
for a few bruises.
You got your bell rung
pretty hard, pal.
You should
get it looked at.
Oh, Mr. Kine,
you worry so.
Get it checked out.
[chuckle] Okay.
Whatever you say.
I'll go.
While I'm there,
I think I'll pay Dotachin
a little visit.
Why would you
team up with Izaya?
[chuckle] Never mind.
I doubt any of us are
following his orders anyway.
You'd better watch your step.
A smart girl like you
has got potential.
Don't waste it
hanging around Izaya.
I know, I know.
Believe me, I know.
[neck cracks]
[chatter]
Whatever you want
to talk about
must be serious.
I bet I know what it is.
It's about that sword,
isn't it?
Y-Yeah, it is.
You sure you want
to talk here?
It's not exactly private.
Uh, um...
I don't care
if someone hears.
What I'm about to say
sounds so crazy,
no one would
believe me anyway.
Really? Is it okay
if I listen in, too, then?
Well, look what the cat
dragged in. How you been?
Don't tell me you're here
to visit Dotachin, too.
W-Why are you here?
Oh, please.
Is that so weird?
Unexpected is more like it.
And since when do you
and Anri know each other?
All right, then,
what are you up to?
What's that look for?
It's scaring me a little.
What did you do
to Mikado and Masaomi?
Did you mess with them?
-[Erika] Anri?
-[Saika] Go ahead. Use me.
I will love him for you.
I understand your concern.
If I were you, I'd be
suspicious of me, too.
I guess you know me
pretty well after all.
Although, if I were you,
I'd take care who I aimed
my inhuman eyes at.
[gasp]
Are you messing with them,
or aren't you?
I've had absolutely nothing
to do with them lately.
I don't believe you!
Too bad
because it's true.
However, I am planning
to mess with them
-in the near future.
-Wha--
It's true. Mikado and Masaomi
have great potential.
They're more interesting
now than ever before.
How should I put it?
It's like the two of them
are walking on a tightrope
strung between two cliffs.
You see the metaphor?
The cliffs, the rope,
their friendship?
As they walk along,
another rope is wound
around both their necks.
If one of them
stumbles and falls,
he'll drag the other
right down with him.
Even if one of them
grabbed that tightrope
at the last second,
it would only tighten the noose
around the other's neck.
Talk about suspenseful.
-[quivering]
-Can you imagine
the reactions
of the people watching?
I bet some would
charge admission.
Others would get on the rope
and try bouncing them off.
And the do-gooders would be
at the bottom of the cliff
spreading rescue mats
around. Hilarious.
-[Saika] Use me.
-You know what I'd do?
I'd set fire to both
ends of the tightrope
and just sit back and watch.
[voices chattering]
-[Saika] Use me.
-Really?
Why would you
want to do that?
Curiosity, I guess.
I'd like to see what they'd do
in a situation like that.
No way.
I can love everyone for you.
[Anri] Shut up!
I don't get it.
Why are you
telling me all this?
What good does
any of this do you?
What good does it do, you ask?
I told you once before.
I love all human beings,
no matter
how horrible they are.
In my opinion,
that gives me certain rights,
like messing with their heads
if I want to.
For example, there's a girl
with a grudge against me
who tried to kill me once.
But I don't hate her.
I still love her
like any other human.
[Shingen] Now, this girl
you just heard about
has no clue whatsoever she's
loved as much as she is.
And even though she's
currently, quote-unquote,
working for the man
she tried to kill,
all she can think about is
finding a way to hurt him.
That's why today,
she's come here,
to the home of another girl
who's also working
for the same man.
[doorbell rings]
Well, well.
How's it going, Manami?
What'cha doing here?
I just came by
to mess with Izaya.
Sounds like more work
than it's worth.
You got anything
special in mind?
Thirty minutes later,
she's outside
and on her merry way,
heading toward the city.
And then...
this girl also
goes for a walk
-with a spring in her step.
-[giggling]
However, this girl finds
that she can't move at all.
She's trembling,
shocked, confused.
[Anri, panting]
He's out of his mind.
I have to use Saika now,
or else Mikado
and Masaomi could--
[Saika] And here I thought
we were getting closer.
[Anri] But then,
if I gave Saika's power
to someone as twisted as him,
what would happen?
[Saika] Your mother knew
how to handle me better.
-She would take care of--
-Shut up!
Don't give me that look.
You have no right
to criticize me.
You gave your friends
the cold shoulder.
Yep, you had
Mikado and Masaomi wrapped
around your little finger.
-That's not--
-Forgive me for being blunt,
but in my opinion,
you should have used
Saika on both of them.
[gasp] That's so wrong!
How can you say that?
I'm sorry.
You think it's wrong?
Oh, I don't know.
If we're talking about
normal humans, yes.
But they can't do
the things that you can.
Listen, whatever
you think you are,
you're most definitely
not human.
-[gasp]
-You gave up your humanity
when you chose
to become one with Saika.
That's how the deal works.
And despite you not
being human anymore,
here you are pretending
to brood like a human,
doing nothing even when your
dearest friends are in danger.
I swear to Christ,
if you make my friend cry,
I'll take a soldering iron
to your eyes.
[chuckle] Oh, Erika,
as a fellow human,
I love this side of you.
So, out of respect for that,
I'll back off.
Glad to hear it,
but if you think
you're off the hook
with me, you're wrong.
It's been fun chatting,
ladies,
but I'm late for a date
with a cranial nerve exam.
Yeah? Then make sure
they take a good look
while they're poking around.
If your brain looks
like moldy cauliflower,
you're screwed.
[quivering]
Oh, my God. Here it co--
Take it easy.
Don't let him get to you.
He's just pushing
your buttons is all.
But, Erika, another second,
and I would have
slashed him and--
But you didn't,
so relax, okay?
You could be
a demon reincarnated,
one that wiped
everything out
millions of years ago,
but I wouldn't care.
I'd forgive you for it.
[Shingen] They say
the bonds between women
can't be broken.
But they also say
a woman's worst enemy
is another woman.
This one and this one
will be enemies.
They just haven't met yet.
[Shingen] This person,
who still can't bring
herself to call me Dad,
is also a woman.
I've never been
so exhausted. I'm done.
Sorry I left you out there.
I should have helped you
sort them out.
No, it's okay. You need
all the rest you can get.
Things went downhill
pretty fast
after everyone decided
to take a nap.
People fighting over
who'd room with whom,
especially Namie and Mika.
What a drag.
Those two are always going
for each other's throats.
So how did that turn out?
Neither wanted the other
to sleep with Seiji.
In the end, I managed
to convince them
to sleep in my old room.
I said, "This way, you can
keep an eye on each other."
[Shinra] So where
did you put Seiji?
The same room as your dad.
[snoring]
[Seiji] He wears that thing
even while he's sleeping?
[Celty] Everyone's
down for the count.
It took all night to get
everyone's stories,
but I managed
to get them all.
You've got a heart
of gold, Celty.
What are you
buttering me up for?
Nothing. I mean it.
You act more human
than most humans.
That's why you're so kind.
And that's why I worry.
What if one day
you get fed up with us?
What if you do,
and then turn into a monster,
and then destroy the planet?
-That's never going to ha--
-Wait. Listen.
Even if you decide
to wipe everyone out,
I'll be there
to help you pull the plug.
I don't care
if I'm the last human on Earth.
As long as I can die
in your arms, I'll be happy.
Ow.
Putting it all on me
again, eh?
Like making me
the leader of a guild?
What were you thinking?
Yeah, I kind of
forced that on you.
It's fine.
I'm happy to go along
with whatever you're up to.
Just get better
because I miss you.
That makes me so happy!
And overjoyed, ecstatic,
jubilant, on Cloud 9!
-[giggling]
-[crack]
Oh! Oh, that was a mistake.
Easy does it, cowboy.
Now what?
You have all the info,
but where do you start?
I guess
with Kasane Kujiragi.
Mm.
And the first thing
I'm going to do
is make her pay
for what she did to you.
Kasane Kujiragi.
[Shingen] She's consumed
by thoughts of her enemy,
who, as it turns out,
is enjoying her first
taste of freedom
this very second.
That's a lot
of party favors.
Actually, they're all for me.
As most of you already know,
her name isn't
Kasane Kujiragi.
Her real name isn't
important, though.
Now, this may
come as a shock,
but Ruri Hijiribe's mother
and Kasane are half-sisters,
Kasane being
considerably younger.
The grandmother
Ruri loved so much
took Kasane
after she was born--
this is a child that wasn't
her husband's, mind you--
and sold her to an old man
called Jinnai Yodogiri.
How diabolical!
The old man trained Kasane
from a young age
to run his business,
forcing her to lead a life
preying on humans
and monsters alike.
After Yodogiri died,
she continued
to run the business,
using stand-ins for him,
because running that business
was all she knew
in the world.
When she found out
about Ruri,
who shared the same blood,
yet was pursuing
her dreams freely,
it made her jealous.
Apparently,
even an emotionless
husk of a woman
like her had dreams
smoldering somewhere deep down
at the bottom of her heart.
[phone rings]
[Seitaro] It's me. Look,
I can't seem to get
through to Yodogiri.
Is something wrong?
President Yodogiri was
in a car accident earlier.
You're kidding!
What about that job
I hired him for?
I'll be taking care
of that now.
Oh. Okay.
I guess that's fine.
Just watch your back
out there.
Nebula might try
something funny
like yesterday.
Thank you for your concern,
Mr. Yagiri.
[Shingen] Her enemy is
her friend is her enemy.
Thanks to Izaya Orihara,
Kasane was able
to experience freedom
for the first time
in her life.
-[giggling]
-Besides,
today, she had more
important things to do.
Why waste it thinking
about where her enemy was
or what he was up to?
Today, she would dream.
Even though her face
shows no emotion,
inside, she's filled
with bliss.
She wonders where
she could go next
wearing her new cat ears.
A cat cafe,
or maybe a butler cafe.
Her bliss is undeniable.
No way. That's what
Mikado told you?
I know, right?
That whole thing about
tearing the Dollars down
and starting over,
and keeping everything
a secret from Anri?
This is not going
to end well for anyone.
I mean, destroying the--
He's not thinking straight.
You care. That's what
I love about you.
Huh--uh--
You're amazing.
I hope you know that.
Oh, what is with you
all of a sudden?
I mean, when you
talk like that, I--
Well, now you've got me
all frisky!
[panting]
I'm going to go see
if Anri's logged
into the chatroom yet.
I am so sorry,
but we completely sold out
of all the stock we had
a little while ago.
Oh, you did?
[Erika] Hey, you mind
running an errand for me?
If all of us girls
are wearing cat ears
when Dotachin wakes up,
man, the look on his face
will be priceless.
[thinking] Erika.
I couldn't care less
whether you're human or not.
I know you, Anri, and how
sweet and caring you are.
I mean, look at you. You care
about your friends so much,
it's all you can do
to keep from crying.
It's all good, girl.
I have to find another shop.
-[heartbeat]
-[gasp]
What is that?
It's been a long time, Anri.
Yeah, Haruna. I guess so.
I've been looking
all over for Takashi,
but I didn't expect
to run into you.
Do you mind
if we take a little walk?
-[gasp]
-I don't care
if we have a fight
out in the open,
but you, I know.
You wouldn't like that
one little bit, would you?
[Kururi] Either way,
I think what happened today
will revolutionize
the world.
The majority of folks
tooling around in cyberspace
might think this stuff's
all just a prank,
but not me.
I know for a fact
it's for real.
Sure,
they don't show up on TV,
and the online news outlets
always pixelate them.
But it's not like that
on social media.
People are uploading
videos and photos
like there's no tomorrow.
Every day there's more.
And today of all days,
right here at Ikebukuro,
finally something's appeared!
[Mairu] I'm scared.
There's nothing
to be scared of.
As long as we stick together,
we can overcome anything,
even death,
as long as I'm with you.
Yay! Kiss! Ouch!
I got pinched!
[Celty] Hi, there.
Long time no see.
No Saika today?
Maybe she's busy.
I think I'll try
texting her.
How's it going, Setton?
I guess maybe you haven't
heard the latest news, huh?
I guess that figures.
I mean, it's only been
about 30 minutes or so
since it popped up
in everyone's news feeds.
Wait. What did I miss?
"You might want
to turn on the news.
It's the top story."
Where are you going?
What's wrong?
[Kururi] The Noontime News
is about to start.
I'm sure you can
catch the story
-on the Daiou Network.
-What's up?
They're running
a special on it.
Do you guys mind
if I switch to the news
-for a second?
-[Walker] Are you kidding?
Of course not.
It's yours and Dr. K's TV.
Go ahead.
Uh, we're live here
at the scene
outside Ikebukuro Station.
Around 11:00 this morning,
just outside the east exit,
commuters made
a ghoulish discovery.
According to witnesses,
a woman's head
was thrown by someone
into the bushes.
Huh?
[Manami] I came to steal
something Izaya's got
stashed away here.
That's all.
I'm the only one
here right now,
so you'll have to get past me.
If you're worried
about getting in trouble,
just say I told you he said
for me to come grab it.
[laughing] Even if I do,
what do I get
for letting you?
You'll get your freedom back.
Really?
I don't know the details,
but you're looking
for someone, right?
[giggling] Come in.
Take whatever you want.
[Shingen] That's right.
This young lady stole the head
right out from under his nose
and exposed it to the world
out of spite!
-[chatter]
-Holy--
Uh...
-[crash]
-Huh?
-[Saburo] Oh, shit. She's down.
-[Walker] Celty, are you okay?
-[Shingen] Yep, women.
-Hey, Celty! Celty, wake up!
Doesn't matter
if they're human or not.
Women will be women.
If you're watching
and you're one of them,
I'm done talking.
But if you're a man,
you'd better watch
your step, pal.
Hmm?
♪ [singing in Japanese]
[Mairu]
It's mind-boggling,
earth-shattering,
totally unexpected!
There's a head and a cat
and Izaya droning on and on,
as usual.
Hey, Kururi,
who was this person again?
Looks kind of familiar.
[Kururi] Next time:
All in the Same Boat.