♪ [theme song playing]
♪ [man singing in Japanese]
You know Mikado Ryugamine?
He's our boss now, asshole!
[chuckles]
[growls]
I'll prove the kind of love
she and I have, anyone can have.
Stop talking like you're--
I'm kinda looking forward
to this next part.
Like, what if after I die,
there's something else?
♪ [singing resumes]
♪ [ends]
No! No!
You don't have to!
Sorry. I do.
[gun fires]
[Masaomi]
Mikado!
[grunting]
[crowd exclaiming]
[Chikage]
He got a death wish,
or somethin'?
Izaya doesn't care
if he dies.
He wants society
to reject Shizuo.
If he beats him, cool.
If he dies,
then Shizuo's a murderer.
No matter what happens,
he gets his way.
You sound
like you know him.
He and I are
two of a kind.
Keep pushing.
You're almost there!
Bust in there
and possess everyone!
That's it!
[groans]
[grunting]
[crowd gasping]
[gasps]
[grunts]
[yelling]
[crowd exclaiming]
[man]
Whoa!
[groaning]
[metal banging, scraping]
[coughing]
[laughing]
Do it. You monst--
[crowd whispering]
[knife clattering]
Varona...
You are human, Shizuo.
This job for beast. Not you.
Don't do it! Killin' him
ain't gonna do you no good.
Do not worry for me.
Since child,
have always loved to kill.
I am beast.
[chuckles]
You're so not a beast.
You're just a human.
An ordinary human.
[grunting]
Harasho! Hey!
Lookit! Ain't that Shizuo?
Where?
[crowd yelling]
Oh!
[Simon]
Hey!
[crowd exclaiming]
Goddamn it! Now, Haruna!
Possess everyone! Do it!
Yes, Mother.
I love you...
Get off me, bitch!
[crowd clamoring,
people screaming]
[Mikado]
Weird...
I don't feel any pain.
It's so dark.
Is it gonna be
like this, forever?
[Celty]
I know what I have to do.
[Mikado] Huh?
[Celty]
Before I leave this city,
I will undo all the trouble
associated with my body.
[Mikado]
Am I still alive?
But... how?
[Celty]
Cleaning up this mess
is the least I can do,
to atone for all
the chaos I have caused.
[Mikado]
Celty?
[Masaomi]
Mikado? Hey!
Mikado! Talk to me!
Masaomi?
You're alive! Thank God!
The hell...?
What is that?
You're Celty, aren't you?
Your name is Mikado.
Is that correct, human?
Do not take
my existence here
as proof that there is hope
for you after death.
The presence of my body
in this city seems
to have influenced you
negatively, I'm afraid.
Before I take my leave,
I have some parting words.
You're leaving?
But you--
[Anri] Mikado!
Masaomi!
Anri?
Saki, what are you doing?
[all panting]
I found you,
at last, my beloved.
[groaning]
Varona!
Hey! Her no conscious now.
But when wake, I make
nice pot green tea, da ?
The hell'd she do that for?
Well, if you ask me,
maybe she was tryin'
to keep your ass
from gettin'
locked up for murder.
[sighs]
Sorry, Varona.
I'm still not as strong
as I should be.
All right.
What the hell's goin' on?
It's a friggin' mess.
Did Celty do all this?
Uh? Shinra?
If humans died over
a conflict caused by my body,
it would bring me
great pain.
I shall be saving many lives
by leaving here.
This isn't your fault, Celty.
I'm the one
who caused all this!
Then let me ask you, human...
had you not had your encounter
with the Headless Rider,
do you think you still
would have tried to kill
your friend this night?
If it weren't for my presence,
Seiji Yagiri would not have
succumbed to a delusional love.
And Mika Harima would not
have discarded the face
she was born with.
How can you say that?
My love's not delusional!
The fact remains
that my presence here
has caused nothing
but disruption,
to this city and the lives
of all its inhabitants.
You're wrong.
Wait! Listen!
What about all the people here
you saved? People like me?
I am a system,
not a savior.
I serve a higher power,
notifying the chosen
of their impending demise.
I would not expect humans
to know what that means.
Even if you did,
you would not comprehend it.
I shall resume my duties
in my homeland.
[grunts]
To you, Mikado,
whose fate was negatively
affected by my presence,
I bid you farewell.
My obligation here has ended.
Forget you ever saw me.
[Shinra] You were never
all that good at lying, Celty.
[neighs]
What's wrong, Shooter?
Get going.
[Shinra]
I think what you really mean
is, "Come on, Shooter, go!
If you don't, you'll show
everyone that I've been
faking it this whole time!"
Right?
[neighing]
And who might you be, human?
Here's what that means...
"Why did you have
to be here?
Seeing you makes
my leaving more painful.
I thought, if I acted
like I forgot everything,
it would make it easier
for you to forget me."
Right?
What is this? I know not
what you speak about.
I'm sure it's true
you got your memories
of your former life back,
but there's also
something else I'm sure of.
That you haven't forgotten
the life you had with me
in this city.
How ridiculous.
See, what you said right there
is a dead give-away.
Your kindness
shines through again.
It's kind of blinding,
actually.
You're thinking,
"Stop making this hard!
I'm not supposed
to be in this city!
All I want is to stop
the trouble I've caused
and leave without
causing any more pain
than I have to!
If I made everyone think
I lost my memories,
it'd be easier
for them to let me go!
But you want to ruin my plan
and you're the one
who should forget me the most!"
Nonsense.
Aw, come on, Celty.
Don't be like that.
Silence, human! Be gone!
I've had quite enough
of your prattling.
[yelps, muffled yelling]
Go! Go! Go on, Shooter!
[whinnying]
Go!
[neighs]
[footsteps departing]
Wait, Celty!
Please come back!
Don't go! You can't go!
Don't leave us!
[whinnying]
Hey!
Shizuo?
The hell was that?
Wait, was that Celty?
It was, indeed! Good timing!
Yeah. I saw you come up here,
so I followed you.
What the hell's
goin' on around here?
This and that. Anyway,
you're going to help me
be the bad guy now.
Say what?
Remember that promise
you made me,
back in high school?
Hm?
I have to do something
incredibly cruel to Celty.
She's the kindest
person I know,
so I'm pretty sure she'll
forgive me for doing it.
Well?
I'm ready. Come on,
kick my ass into orbit!
Here goes! Better not
hate me for doing this!
[screaming]
Oh, Shooter,
don't be so grumpy.
It had to end this way.
I have all
of my memories back now.
If I stayed here
and lived with these people,
I'd only cause them
even more suffering
and heartache.
[neighs]
Yes, Shooter.
It hurts, a lot.
I want Shinra to forget me,
but I don't want to forget him.
Hey!
Huh?
What the--? [stammering]
What are you doing up here?
[whinnying]
Grab on!
Celty... Sorry!
[gasps]
No!
[whinnying]
Shinra...
[echoing]
Shinra!
Shinra! Come on, wake up!
Don't die!
Take it easy, Celty.
I'm an injured man, remember?
You dumb, stupid idiot!
Ow!
You're the dumbest,
stupidest idiot in the world!
OW! Stop! Okay!
That hurts, Celty!
What are you thinking?
You could've died!
Why are you such an idiot?
Sorry for being
selfish again.
I got in the way
of your Dullahan-ing duties.
But, if I didn't risk my life,
it wouldn't be fair, would it?
Like I said,
you're an idiot.
[Mikado] I guess...
maybe I wanted people
to hate me.
If everyone
thought I was evil,
I guess I figured someone
would have to come stop me.
[Mikado]
The three of us
had changed so much.
[Anri] We promised,
when we were together again,
we'd tell each other
our secrets.
[Mikado]
Yeah, we did.
[Masaomi] Okay, hold it!
When'd you guys do that?
Why am I always the last
to hear about these things?
Whatever!
So, who wants to go first?
Are you kidding? You!
Anri's secret's for dessert!
If we do this,
we're doin' it right!
[chuckles]
We changed a lot.
[car horn honking]
[gasps]
[laughing]
[Mikado]
Mr. Nasujima?
[gasps, grunts]
[groans]
[both gasp]
You! You ruined everything!
[grunting repeatedly]
[Masaomi]
Mikado!
[Anri screaming]
With that,
the night was over.
But even after the sun came up,
shadows covered the city.
The news said it was some
kind of natural phenomenon
caused by a freak sandstorm.
So, how come y'all got stuck
in this goop, but not me?
Didn't think shit
would end like this.
Oh, yeah? I didn't think
my fight with you
would end with me
stuck to a goddamn pole.
[phone ringing]
By afternoon, the shadows
started to go away.
[groaning]
[Kine]
Leave it. Don't want
to bleed out, do ya?
Mr. Kine?
It's 50/50 you survive,
so don't get your hopes up.
[chuckles]
You might want to thank
the lady in the back
before you croak.
I mean, she did help
carry your ass to the car.
Don't get the wrong idea.
I wasn't trying to save you.
I just wanted to be around
when you died.
If I was smart, I would've
dumped you in the lobby
of the nearest ER.
But I bet you'd rather see
my underground doc, right?
Yeah. Just so long
as he's not in the city.
I want to get as far
away from here as I can.
If I'm to die,
the last thing I want
is that monster
hanging around my deathbed.
[woman]
The retrieval unit
has the head,
and they're on their way
to main office in Chicago.
They're being extra careful.
Once they deliver it,
it'll be filed away
as a special human specimen.
Thanks for
the update, pumpkin!
Well, Namie,
got any plans for the future?
What do you mean?
What future?
Your obsession
with that head is an asset.
An asset that could take you
far at a place like Nebula!
What is this? Are you
trying to recruit me now?
Yeah, that should
be pretty obvious.
If you can't tell a job offer
when you hear one, then,
you know, maybe you
should have your head
examined for a change!
[choking]
Crushing...
Adam's... apple...
with... thumbs!
[Mikado]
Now that the chaos was over,
everyone was busy,
searching for closure.
Are you sure you want
to come with me?
Yup! Wherever you go, I go!
That's how it is!
Right. But why'd you
tell me they were taking
the head to Chicago?
You could've just
kept quiet about it,
gone there and destroyed it,
or whatever you want
to do with it.
I know, but I'd rather
go there with you, Seiji!
I'm still in love
with that head, you know.
I'm not in love with you.
But, if it's okay,
I can love you
like you were family.
[laughing]
Die!
[horn honking repeatedly]
Oh, gosh. Ms. Kujiragi?
My apologies, in advance,
for what I'm about to say.
I happen to be
quite jealous of you.
Huh?
I've also decided to steal
an opportunity from you.
The chance to atone
for your sins as Hollywood,
the serial killer.
This is both
my crime against you
and my punishment for you.
But I have to turn myself in.
You'd be wasting your time.
I assure you,
I have my claws deep within
both the police department
and the media.
Please wait a minute!
Who are you?
What would you call
someone who is extremely
jealous of you?
A villain, perhaps?
I almost forgot! You hear
about how they arrested
Ruri Hijiribe's stalker?
Yeah. His name's
Kisuke Adabashi.
He tried to hit her
with a truck,
but a fan of hers
was passin' by
and beat him half to death.
Then, dumped his ass
in front
of the police station!
I would've tied
his balls to my fender
and dragged him to death!
[both laughing]
Well, at least things are
back to normal around here.
See you tomorrow!
Details of return home
are complicated.
I have issues with Father.
I must rectify them on own.
I won't bug you
about it, but...
seein' as how
you're my trainee,
if you ever need
to talk, hit me up.
If ever possibility arise
to return to city again,
I challenge you to duel.
But a duel of word
and promise I will speak to you
within inch of life!
After duel,
I wish to experience
joy of living
in this place again,
if would be so kind.
Sure.
[whinnying]
So, uh, Celty,
you still have all
your head's memories, right?
'Cause this time,
you weren't asleep
when it got cut off--
[screams]
[whinnying]
It doesn't matter
anymore, does it?
Hm?
I'm going to be
with you forever.
Aw... Celty!
Would you stop!
Don't do that out here!
People will see us and--
[man] Yo.
I don't care
if the whole world sees us!
You know that!
Well, well.
The monster's got a boyfriend!
Sexin' it up
in a "no stopping" zone
just earned you
a big, fat ticket.
Huh? What's going on?
Is something wrong?
[sirens blaring]
Hang on. Don't die.
Huh? [screaming]
Oh, my God!
Slow down, Celty!
[Mikado] Okay...
I guess now, I'll tell you
what happened to me.
[groaning]
[panting]
[screaming]
Uh-uh. I won't
let you have Takashi.
H-Haruna?
[laughing]
But I thought you
were under my control.
Of course! I know you like it
when I'm all submissive!
[gasps, whimpering]
Wait, Takashi!
Mm? [gasps]
Look! It's him! The boss
of the red-eyed zombies!
He said he was
gonna hurt Mikarun!
No way! He was sittin'
in the car that ran me over!
What?
[engine revving]
[Saburo]
You guys both sure about him?
Yeah.
Uh-huh.
No, Saburo! Wait!
Shit yeah! Drive this thing
right down his throat!
[gasps]
[crash, tires squealing]
[breathing heavily]
What's going on?
Where the hell am I?
[Haruna] We're in one
of Izaya Orihara's hideouts.
Nobody comes here.
It's soundproofed.
So, no matter how violent
our love-making gets,
no one will hear.
[whimpering]
Don't worry, Takashi.
I'll take good care of you.
[grunting]
We'll share the pain,
over and over and over again.
[whimpering]
[screaming]
When I open my eyes,
what'll be waiting for me?
Will I have an ordinary life?
You're Aoba Kuronuma,
ain't ya?
You're with the Awakusu.
Let me guess...
You're here to see Mikado
and get your digs in.
What do you want from me?
[laughing]
I guess I'm gettin' old!
Whenever I'm around
you young'uns,
I tend to speak my mind.
Especially around
sneaky little bastards
like yourself.
Yeah, well, if you're worried
about Mikado, don't be.
We got what we wanted,
so we're not gonna mess
with him anymore.
Good. Glad to hear it.
I don't know
if you're a Dollar
or a Blue Square these days,
but if you pull
any more of your shit,
I'll make you regret
you ever squirted
out your mama.
It was good talkin'
with you, Kuronuma.
Get on home now.
Or, will my life
be extraordinary?
Well, now, that's a bummer.
I was hopin'
to thank him, in person,
seein' as how
he risked his life
to save you and all.
Sorry. He's still
unconscious, though.
Maybe tomorrow, then.
Anyway, what's up
with you guys. You like him?
Yes, but I'm still trying
to sort my feelings out.
Oh, yeah? You sure
they're your own feelings?
Yes, I'm sure.
You don't have
to worry about that!
Is this is the life
I'm supposed to come back to?
How did I end up here?
And why?
Was there a point
to anything I did?
Or, wasn't there?
[Masaomi]
Mikado? Mikado!
In the end,
I realized something.
Mikado!
What's out there...
that's reality.
It's not ordinary
or extraordinary,
but I can reach out
and touch it.
It's real.
That's what
I'm waking up to right now.
[monitor beeping]
[moaning]
Welcome back!
Yeah. We missed you, man!
This right here... is real.
[Kururi]
I cannot believe
how quiet it is here.
But I'm sure
it'll fill up again soon,
with all kinds
of unsavory characters.
[Mairu]
I can't wait!