["Headhunt" by Okamoto's]
[man singing in Japanese]
♪ ♪
IZAYA: And that's why
he's such a noble choice.
Like a sacrificial lamb.
MASAOMI: I said shut it‐‐
‐ This definitely is not
Shizuo's handiwork.
Shizuo
wouldn't have stopped there.
‐ If you want this fight,
bring it.
I'm all in.
‐ It's bad.
That boy is way too trusting.
ANRI: I've seen
this girl somewhere.
They're wanting someone
to kidnap Rio's friend?
♪ ♪
[Kyohei and Chikage grunting]
‐ Kabaddi. Kabaddi.
Kabaddi. Kabaddi.
Kabaddi. Kabaddi. Kabaddi.
[fast‐paced jazz music]
♪ ♪
GIRL: I guess I joined
the Dollars about a month ago.
I still don't really know
that much about them,
but I'm posting this
because I thought
you guys might find it useful.
Hope it helps.
‐ I've had enough!
MAN: A color gang
whose sphere of influence
has rapidly expanded
in the last year.
MAN: That's the Dollars.
MAN: Our team has no color.
BOY: We live
hidden in the darkness,
obscuring our true selves.
Our uniform is the naked body.
GIRL: Or some enigmatic
secret organization.
BOY: And some call us
a bunch of lowlifes.
IZAYA: Read this now!
I don't have the stones
to kidnap her,
but if anyone out there does,
go for it.
It's the girl sitting
second from the left.
It's all set.
Ball's in your court.
Which path will you take,
Mikado?
GIRL: Yeah.
GIRL: Hey.
[laughter]
‐ What's this about?
‐ Huh?
RIO: This is us, right?
NON: Yeah, it is.
[cell phone whistling]
‐ Oh?
[all gasp]
‐ Found you.
[all panting]
MAN: Uh‐huh.
[laughter]
[men laughing]
‐ [panting heavily]
Just making sure,
but you're Non, right?
Your boyfriend's been getting
a little carried away
on our turf lately,
so we've been thinking
we ought to get some payback.
‐ You mean Rocchi?
‐ Yeah, Rocchi, Bocchi‐‐
whatever his name is,
Ms. Bitchy.
We'd like you to come along
with us for a little bit.
‐ I understand,
and I'll go with you guys
quietly.
Also, could you let the others
just walk out of here?
‐ Non, there's no way
we'll let you do that.
‐ Yeah, but‐‐
‐ Sorry,
but that's not gonna happen.
If we let the other girls go,
they're gonna call the cops
on us.
That's not gonna fly.
[girls gasp,
men snickering]
MIKADO: Hold on!
ALL: Huh?
‐ Is that Mikado?
Why?
‐ What‐‐
what exactly are you doing?
‐ Nothing that's any of
your business, brat. Shoo.
‐ It is my business!
‐ Huh?
‐ 'Cause I'm a member
of the Dollars also!
[men groan]
I saw that email
and came straight here,
but this is wrong.
How can you go around
taking girls hostage?
‐ Yeah, yeah.
Whatever.
[Mikado grunts]
♪ ♪
If you really are
one of the Dollars,
then you ought to know this‐‐
it's not like there's any rules
against taking girls hostage.
Hell,
we don't even have any rules
in the Dollars, right?
MAN: Right.
The Dollars have free rein.
MASAOMI: Not to mention,
you can't force anyone
to follow an order either.
GIRL: Even if
you happen to be the founder.
MIKADO: He's right.
I'm the one
who set things up this way.
But still, all this?
This is the last thing
I wanted us to become.
The Dollars
would never do this stuff.
We don't go taking girls
against their will.
Doing something that pathetic‐‐
it's not us!
‐ Whatever.
[tires screech]
Hey, can't have that kid
call the cops on us,
so you guys stay behind
and pound him till he's dust,
yeah?
‐ Hey, hold on.
We'd rather get time
with the chicks
than beat up some dude.
‐ I'll hang on to 'em for you.
Don't sweat it.
You ought to be able
to make short work
of a twerp like him anyway.
‐ Humph.
‐ Asshole.
‐ Yo, there, dawg!
You remember me from before?
Yo. Yo!
We ran into each other
about a year ago, yo.
You were with that guy
who busted my ex's cell,
if that rings a bell.
‐ [groaning]
‐ You know,
I found something out
after joining the Dollars,
yo.
I heard about this guy
named Izaya Orihara.
Turns out
the bastard's kind of famous.
[Mikado gasps confusedly]
[Izaya laughing maniacally]
Mother‐‐
Man.
So you knew someone famous.
Big whoop.
Just 'cause he's some kind
of big‐shot don't make you one,
got it?
Or was it something else?
Were you thinking
that just 'cause
you joined the Dollars,
that means
you're badass like us?
Bitch!
MIKADO: Oh, I remember.
That's him.
‐ Having wimps like you
in the Dollars
makes the rest of us look
like a bunch of candy‐asses!
[grunts]
MIKADO: That piece of shit.
‐ Hey, Masaomi.
Aren't you gonna go?
‐ And where am I going?
‐ Wherever your friends are,
of course.
‐ [sighs]
‐ That phone call with Izaya
just now...
you sounded really mad at him.
[Masaomi gasps]
Are you still scared?
You don't want your friends
to wind up hating you again.
Isn't that right?
‐ There's a little more to it.
You know,
when it comes down to it,
I guess that is
what it's all about.
AKABAYASHI: There are
all kinds of people
who are with the Dollars
these days.
Even an old guy like me
can get his hands
on a boatload of info
on the kids,
just by signing up
for the mailing list.
IZAYA: That might be more useful
than an information broker
who never picks up
when you call.
♪ ♪
SHIKI: If those guys weren't
even going after Hollywood,
would there really be
any reason to kill them?
Right now, if our guys‐‐
no, if number two's henchmen
were killed,
who'd be the one
who'd benefit from it?
Our parent organization,
the Medei Group,
is at a critical point
in reconciling
with the Asuki Group.
Is this an Asuki plot
to distance themselves
from the Medei?
Or maybe there's someone around
who's against
Mikiya taking over as boss.
[high‐pitched ringing]
[sighs]
[door handle rattles]
Hmm?
‐ Hey there, Celty!
Welcome home!
And I'm glad
you're safe and sound too.
Are you all right?
You didn't get a boo‐boo
anywhere,
did you?
‐ I'm okay.
Thank you for asking,
Dr. Kishitani.
‐ That's good.
Glad to hear it.
I'll go make you
some hot chocolate, okay?
‐ [gasps]
‐ Hello, Ms. Akane.
I'm glad that you're safe.
‐ I'm so sorry.
‐ Hold on, there.
You should apologize
to your parents first.
You better prepare yourself
for some punishment.
A slap across the cheek,
at least.
‐ Huh?
What you doing there,
Akabayashi?
Maybe
you don't get the situation
we're in right now.
‐ I'm gathering info,
if you got to know,
about what's going on
in the city.
‐ So that's what you're doing.
Here I thought
you were texting some chick.
‐ Still,
it can't be coincidence.
A lot goes on in Ikebukuro,
but not like this.
‐ Huh?
‐ And if it isn't a coincidence,
if we really do have some people
hanging out around here
who are serious about raising
all kinds of hell,
then that means it'll soon be
our turn to do what we do,
doesn't it, Mr. Aozaki?
‐ Looks like
Shizu‐chan's still on the lamb
somewhere out there.
He should give in
and fight back already.
It's annoying
how he can be so coolheaded
when you least expect it.
[both grunting]
‐ Nothing bad happened
to my father or grandpa, did it?
Shizuo Heiwajima didn't do
anything to them, did he?
‐ Huh?
‐ [gasps]
I knew it!
Please, you have to tell me
what he did to them.
‐ Nothing.
They're fine, I promise.
No reason to worry
your little head over it.
‐ It's like I thought.
I should've just killed him
myself when I had the chance.
‐ What? Young miss,
what did you just say?
[door handle rattles]
‐ Excuse me!
I'm here for a pickup!
‐ Good timing.
I'll be right there.
‐ I've got the car
parked out front
whenever you're ready.
♪ ♪
‐ Thank you for the assistance.
I'll let you know
if anything happens.
‐ [groans]
[both grunting]
‐ When Akane mentioned Shizuo
earlier,
I'm sure
I saw Mr. Shiki stiffen up.
What was that about?
‐ It seems Shizuo's on the run
from the Awakusu group
over some kind
of misunderstanding,
but the real problem
is that it was Izaya
who put the wrong idea
in their heads.
‐ Great, so now
he's involved with this?
‐ Apparently.
Unless
there's somebody out there
pretending to be Izaya
or something.
‐ I don't get the feeling
Izaya would be an easy guy
to impersonate.
‐ You have a point‐‐
[explosion booms]
Get down, Celty!
It's got to be some terrorist.
[men grunting and yelling]
MAN: What the shit?
‐ [gasps]
MAN: What the hell, man?
MAN: Ah, I can't see!
MAN: Where's Ms. Akane?
Ms. Akane!
MAN: What is going on?
MAN: Oh, shit.
MAN: Where'd she go?
MAN: Somebody stop him already!
‐ I'm going.
‐ I'll see you later, then.
Careful, okay?
♪ ♪
[Cóiste‐Bodhar neighs]
‐ Huh?
The Black Rider!
[Cóiste‐Bodhar neighs]
That's jackpot.
[both groaning]
[both grunting]
ANRI: [echoing] Mikado?
Mikado!
[Mikado groans]
Can you hear my voice?
Please hang in there, Mikado.
‐ Huh? Why are you here?
‐ Die, you monster!
[whimpering]
Not again.
‐ What's going on?
‐ It's nothing, Mikado.
I'm relieved, though.
You're not hurt too bad?
‐ No.
[pensive piano music]
[gasps]
[men groaning]
What happened?
Oh, never mind that, Anri.
It's not important anyway.
‐ Thanks.
But now let's get you looked at.
‐ I'm all right, really.
What's important
is that I get to field
number two at Raira.
‐ What?
‐ Sorry.
I've just got to get there
no matter what.
‐ I think you should let
the police take it from here.
‐ If we get the cops involved
in all this,
those guys might snap,
and who knows
what they'll do then?
Besides that, it'd put Kyohei
and the others on the spot.
♪ ♪
‐ Then I'm coming with you,
Mikado.
‐ But, Anri...
‐ I want to rescue
Rio and her friends
just as much as you do.
Besides, I'm hoping
I'll be able to lend a hand.
‐ All right, then.
We'll go there together.
♪ ♪
[tires screech]
VARONA: They are not
calling police.
That girl and boy are fools.
Now I will be able
to dispose of girl with glasses
well before
the police are involved.
SLOAN: Varona, do you copy?
‐ Affirmative.
SLOAN: I have our target.
Akane Awakusu.
Unharmed.
No one has followed us.
‐ Excellent work.
Send me directions
to field two at Raira,
and please move the truck
to that area.
We will be accomplishing
our task today in one swoop.
We can focus
on subduing the Black Rider
as we please, after.
It is fortunate.
♪ ♪
SAKI: Don't worry.
Those two friends of yours
will never hate you,
no matter what.
‐ It's easy for you to say.
You don't know Mikado or Anri.
‐ I don't, it's true.
That's okay.
After all, I know you,
don't I?
And if you chose
to be friends with them,
then it'll be fine.
[Masaomi sighs]
I might be your girlfriend,
Masaomi,
but I can't be your friend
like they are.
♪ ♪
If your friends do somehow
end up hating you
and then you get really,
really down because of it,
if that ever happens,
I'll take you in my arms
and hold you,
because
that's what girlfriends do.
‐ [sighs]
Saki...
♪ ♪
You know, you're pretty smart.
Thanks a lot, Saki.
Well, then, I'm headed out
to meet my friends.
[Saki giggles]
[both yelling]
[both grunt]
[uncertain piano music]
‐ Sure didn't expect this.
Exactly how tough are you,
man?
If you were at 100%,
I'd be the one
lying on the ground right now.
‐ I don't know.
Given how tough you are,
it could've gone either way.
♪ ♪
I didn't pass out just now,
did I?
‐ Just for a little while.
I'm about to keel over myself.
CHIKAGE: Got you.
But God damn it,
this is the first time
in my life
I ever lost two fights in a row.
‐ Oh, please.
I wouldn't count
the one with Shizuo
if I was you.
Listen,
I won't force you to do this
just 'cause I won,
but could you do me a favor
and pull back your Toramaru guys
for today?
[Chikage scoffs]
Do that,
and I'll use my connections
to find the bastards
who went wild up in Saitama,
and I'll get them
to make it up to you somehow.
‐ So you're gonna sell out
the members of your own gang?
‐ Hey, we're the Dollars.
It's not like we have rules.
If I want to sell out
members I don't like,
nothing's stopping me.
‐ Man, you're such a lowlife.
[laughs]
‐ Well, if I wasn't,
I wouldn't be in the Dollars,
am I right?
[both laugh]
ASANUMA: Enough with
the bromance already, Kadota!
You're gonna make me
blow chunks!
[laughing]
BOY: Kabaddi. Kabaddi.
[Mikado and Anri panting]
‐ It looks like
your driver flunky
and the torture tag team
aren't around.
This is it, Kadota.
It's the last day
you're gonna act like
one of the Dollars' leaders.
‐ When the hell did I act
like any of the higher‐ups?
Give me a break.
‐ Don't try to play things cool
and blow us off, you bastard.
Throwing out
that bullshit attitude‐‐
you really think
you can take us all on?
‐ First off, I don't get why I'd
have to take you guys on at all.
I mean, who are you, anyway?
‐ [gasps]
You know,
this really is my lucky day,
'cause I get to beat the shit
out of the Toramaru and you
all in one shot!
What the hell is that?
[men gasp]
‐ Whoa, a helmet splitter.
That's a classy weapon.
‐ What, this old thing?
I bought it
on a trip to Kamakura.
‐ Yeah,
I think I know that place.
The souvenir shop
at the Great Buddha.
‐ Small world, ain't it?
‐ You bastard!
[grunts]
[groaning]
[men gasping]
‐ Taking you all on
might be a little more
than I can handle right now,
but I'll make damn sure
to shatter the ribs
of the first five
who come at me,
or maybe blind 'em.
‐ And if I end up pitching in,
I'll rip the ears off
another five guys,
so don't go saying
that I didn't warn you.
[both snickering]
MORITA: Hold it right there.
[girls whimpering]
‐ Non!
‐ Sorry about all this,
Rocchi.
I ended up getting caught.
MIKADO: We've got to figure out
a way to get behind them
and save those girls
they've taken hostage.
I'm gonna charge in
and do what I can,
and if my plan doesn't work,
I want you to call the police
right away.
[sword chinks loudly]
[intense percussive music]
What?
Huh? Anri?
What the heck?
ANRI: Please run!
♪ ♪
[Mikado gasps]
‐ B‐b‐bomb!
‐ What was that?
♪ ♪
‐ Hey, guys!
‐ Yumasaki?
[Walker chuckles]
‐ Ooh.
‐ Holy shit!
‐ Huh? What the‐‐
[indistinct chatter]
MAN: They're getting away.
MAN: Girls!
MAN: Get the girls!
MAN: Oh, man!
‐ Yeah! I'm about to go
"Dynasty Warriors"
on this big old trash mob!
I'll be like all "Ranbu Ranbu
Revolution" and stuff!
‐ You dick!
‐ Ready?
Why don't you have a taste
of my pyro‐kinesis?
I didn't learn it
in Ms. Komoe's class,
but I think
it's still gonna work.
[giggles]
[men yelling]
Remember, kiddies,
don't try this at home.
‐ Why are they here?
‐ Well,
after we saw the group email,
we were just gonna hide
and watch you two fight,
but this looks like fun,
so count us in.
[melodic horns honking]
CHIKAGE: How do they
even know I'm here?
[Toramaru cheering
and hollering]
[Chikage yelling]
You bastards had the balls
to lay your hands
on someone else's woman.
I guess that means
you're all ready to die.
That boy appears to be
a mere human.
It's a shame.
‐ If you even touch him,
I swear you'll pay for it.
‐ I have one question.
Give me answer, please.
Are you human or monster?
Which are you?
‐ I'm not a human,
but I'm not a monster either!
The truth is,
I'm just a parasite.
MAN: Hey!
MAN: Come on!
‐ Boss!
MAN: There he is.
‐ Boss, you all right?
‐ Yeah.
MAN: Hey, boss,
we're gonna wipe the floor
with these guys, is that cool?
♪ ♪
‐ Uh, Kadota?
‐ You should stick around
for the fun.
‐ [grunts]
‐ [sighs]
If guys like these
are turning up now,
it might be time
for the Dollars to go.
NEKO: It's bad.
Real bad, Aoba.
They got all buddy‐buddy
after that huge brawl of theirs,
and when these weird guys
came with some hostages,
it got crazy, and then
there was this flash of light
and then a huge fireball!
And then there was
this high school girl
with huge boobs.
I mean, like, really huge‐‐
‐ It sure was stupid of me
to send Neko there
to scope out the situation.
♪ ♪
Is this Anri?
[distant booming]
‐ Huh?
CELTY: What should I do?
I know for a fact
that Akane is inside that truck,
but I can't just rush in
without knowing
what I'm up against.
Still, what's it doing
here of all places?
I wonder where Mikado and Anri
could be right now.
Kabaddi, huh?
‐ Kabaddi. Kabaddi.
CELTY: Looks fun.
Wait.
♪ ♪
["Never Say Never"
by Three Lights Down Kings]
[man singing in Japanese]
♪ ♪
MIKADO: I don't know
if it's the right thing to do,
but to catch up with
this city's extraordinariness
and to face Anri and Masaomi
with my head held high,
it's not like
I have any other choice.
Next time,
"Adversity Makes a Man Wise."