♪ [theme song playing]
♪ [man singing in Japanese]
You got red eyes!
I think whoever the new
Slasher in the city is,
has something to do with me.
The next recruit
in my Saika army
is the guy with the dreads.
[Shinra]
Celty...
The beast got away!
[growling]
♪ [singing continues]
♪ [ends]
[Anri]
There comes a time
in a person's life
when they have
to take a stand.
Those people out there
are Saika's children.
[Kyohei] Saika?
[Anri] Yes.
It's written with the kanji
for "sin" and "song."
You called them "children."
Children of what?
Someone like me.
I don't know who infected them,
but they're controlling them.
[Kyohei]
Okay. So, how's that work?
Mm.
[Anri]
He's in constant conflict,
and soon, he'll have
to take a stand.
He has fun, making
other people fight.
[coughs]
He'll have to take
a stand soon, too.
Look. That's Saika.
[all gasp]
[Anri]
So will I.
[grunting]
I'm alive... barely.
What happened?
Oh, right. I remember.
That beast whacked me
like I was a baseball
and knocked me
into the next building.
[groaning]
Damn monster!
He'll be here soon
to finish me off.
[glass shattering, crunching]
Wish he fell to his death.
[thinking]
No, I don't.
What's the point,
if I don't kill him myself?
There wouldn't be.
No, I came here
to kill that brute...
not run away from him.
[grunting]
[growls]
Well, well!
If it isn't Izaya.
Where are you going
in such a hurry?
Hmm... See that, Egor?
I never thought being
ignored by a young person
could hurt so much.
Till now, that is.
Huh, really?
It's not like
it's the first time
that's happened, though.
Oh, so I should be
used to it by now.
Is that what you're saying?
Is it? Well, I'm not!
My son has,
like, two friends,
and that guy
who just passed us
is one of 'em.
And get this--
he stabbed my boy
when they were little.
Was arrested and everything.
You'd think he'd
at least-- Egor?
Oh, that's great!
Now, you're ignoring me, too!
I'm paying your salary,
mister, so if you-- [screams]
What the hell!
I'm sorry. It wasn't--
It wasn't safe
for you there, sir.
Yes, well, um...
This is a little awkward
after scolding you and all,
but, um...
[clears throat] thanks?
No, not at all.
Now what?
I mean, with him.
It's gone, gone.
My beautiful head is gone.
What a shame. See?
This is what happens
when a man becomes obsessed
with supernatural things.
[Egor] Aren't you worried
that your son will turn out
the same as this guy?
No, Shinra's far too stubborn
to let something like this
get in his way!
For him, it'd be just
another one of life's hurdles
to jump on over!
What's the marker for?
Oh, I just thought
I'd scribble something
ridiculous on his face,
before he came to!
What do you think?
Whiskers? Freckles?
Hmm? I knew it.
You were nicked
by Saika, too, huh?
You don't seem
like you're completely
under its control, though.
That Sonohara girl
probably did it.
Feel anything peculiar?
Yes, and it's something that's
been bugging me for a while.
The kids and grandkids
of another mother
are starting
to make some noise.
Great. As if things
weren't complicated enough.
Look. That is Saika.
[moaning, shrieks]
Wow. Doesn't it hurt
when it does that?
Um, Walker?
Today is the day
foretold in the prophecies!
I knew if I was patient,
I'd get the chance to have
my very own superpower!
Come on, what do I gotta do
to have a Saika, too?
Seriously! I'll train at a dojo
with a master swordsman!
And I'll work hard
to prepare my body and mind
for the day when I have
to fight against the enemy!
Walker, um...
If you have a Saika,
it means you'll be cursed
with her need to love humans.
Humans, huh? 3D ones?
Um, I don't think Saika cares
all that much about the 2D kind,
like in manga and stuff.
[sighs]
Well, that sucks.
On second thought,
you know what?
Forget everything I said.
I don't have a problem
loving 2D characters.
I could do that all day.
But loving the 3D kind
is something I'm just
not interested in.
[sighs]
His obsession with all that
nerdy stuff's mind-blowing.
But this is still
super-awesome!
I just found a gateway
to the 2D world!
A real-live demon sword!
We gotta find Erika,
so she can freak out with me!
Come on, let's hurry up
and go get her!
We're not goin'
anywhere yet.
All right, if Erika's been
possessed by that Saika-thing,
then what?
Think you can
snap her out of it?
Yes. If she's infected,
whoever's controlling her
and the others might be close.
If we can find them,
I should be able
to use my Saika on them
to cancel out
their influence.
Then, everyone will go
back to normal... sort of.
'Kay, then.
Looks like I'm counting
on you this time around.
Sorry.
[thinking]
He's so kind.
His friends, too.
Maybe they're like that
because they spend
so much time with him.
We didn't affect
each other like that.
We didn't change
for the better.
But I want to. That's why
I told everyone about Saika.
Still...
Um...
[all]
Huh?
Aren't you guys
afraid of me?
Oh, wow. The sky's
beautiful tonight.
I love that color.
[Shinra]
I wonder if the three of 'em
made up yet. You think?
Made up?
Who are you talking about?
Those kids
from Raira Academy.
Whenever you
tell me about 'em,
I start thinking
about high school
and how it was for me
and stuff.
Yeah, well,
I guarantee none of them
are as pervy as you!
Oh, come on.
That's so not fair.
I was thinking
how me and my friends
are the opposite
of Mikado and his.
What do you mean?
You know how they each
have their secrets?
And how they're
working really hard
not to give them away?
In my group,
Izaya, Shizuo, and I
never tried to hide
who we really were.
That's the big difference
between our group of friends
and theirs.
Well, that and we didn't
have a girl in our group.
You kind of kept
your distance from us.
To be honest, back then,
I didn't really want to have
anything to do with humans.
I bet things would've
turned out differently,
if you hung out with us.
Can you imagine?
Us four,
the best of friends?
I hope things work out for
Mikado and his friends, though.
I really do.
You jealous of them?
No, not at all.
I've got you in my life,
so I couldn't be happier.
And with an amazing life
like this,
what have I got
to be jealous about?
Why'd you have to get
all mushy about it?
[Shinra]
I feel more comfortable
in dark places these days.
Every shadow I see
is a part of you.
If darkness is a color,
then there's
no one else in the world
with that kind of color
but you.
At least,
not that I know of, anyway.
[car horns honking]
Um, aren't you guys
afraid of me?
Why on earth
would I be afraid
of a puny
little girl like you?
I'm kind of surprised,
but scared? Not so much.
But you should be!
'Cause I'm not human.
[Kyohei]
Seriously?
Yes.
I wonder...
What do you think
Celty'd say to that?
I mean, she's way less human
than you are, that's for sure.
But, still,
everyone here likes her.
Oh, please.
Speak for yourself.
Come on, sis.
Dial it down.
[gasps]
I-I'm sorry, Seiji.
You wanna know why
we're not afraid of Celty?
It's 'cause we know
the kind of person she is.
We've seen what she's done
for us and for others.
What makes her happy and sad.
We're cool with who she is,
just like we're cool
with who you are.
You seem like a good kid.
Besides, you never
gave us any reason
not to trust you... yet.
So, go easy on yourself.
Thank you so much.
I mean it.
Thank you for saying that.
[grunts]
Come on, you! Stop cryin'.
Save that stuff
for when you see Mikado
and Masaomi again. Okay?
[Anri thinking]
I'm going to bring
Mikado and Masaomi
into this group of people,
even if they don't want to.
It might be selfish of me,
but I don't care.
[Saika]
Are you abandoning me?
You'll never escape me,
no matter how hard you resist.
I am supposed
to love humans for you.
Don't forget that.
[Anri] Someday, I hope
you and I will be able
to love people for real.
[Saika]
Are you listening?
Humans are mine.
[Anri]
Suddenly, I felt
closer to Saika.
I had friends,
who accepted me
for who I really am,
and it seemed like
Saika was happy about that.
It could've been
my imagination, though.
I have
an announcement to make!
You are hereby a full-fledged,
official member of our guild!
What guild?
A guild of adventure!
It's something Dr. K whipped up
to get us to work as a team
and fix what's goin' on!
Uh...
What sucks is,
Dr. K got kidnapped.
This mysterious woman
in glasses
shot some wires
out of her hands
and took off with him!
Hang on. Are you talking
about Ms. Kujiragi?
Wait, you know
who Kasane Kujiragi is?
Uh-huh. I talked to her
for a bit. I have her card.
Do you have it on you?
'Cause we could call her!
Oh. I'm sorry, I don't.
It's at my apartment.
Well? Wanna go get it?
Naw, man. We can go
pick it up later.
Getting Erika
is more important now.
[Anri]
Oh! Erika has one, too!
She told her
about her cosplay group.
Ms. Kujiragi wants to try it,
so she gave her her card.
Figures!
[overlapping voices]
I love you.
I am so screwed. What do I do?
Come on, Erika, think!
What do you have that'll save
the heroine of this story?
You've read tons of manga,
so you know there's something
in here you can use!
[gasps, chuckles]
[moaning]
[Takashi]
Shijima, can you tell
which one's Mikado?
A couple look
about his size,
but they're all wearing
those dumb masks.
Well, we'll have them all
under control soon.
Once we do, they can capture
Jinnai Yodogiri for us,
along with his secretary.
Then, what are you
gonna do with them?
If we can get
Yodogiri and Kujiragi
under our control, great.
If not, I'll just
bury 'em somewhere.
[chuckles]
I'll make sure to have
some fun with Kujiragi
before I do, though!
[chuckles]
[thinking] Holy crap!
What do they want with
Mika-roon and Ms. Kujiragi?
She was with Anri
the other day!
Oh, no!
She's infected, too!
Sorry, but I can't
help you now.
Uh-oh! My cover's blown!
You're--
[phone ringing]
What the--?
I thought you said no one had
your number, Haruna. Give it.
Yes, Mother.
[ringing continues]
Well, well!
Haruna? It's me.
Can you talk?
How have you been, Anri?
[gasps]
You're such a bad girl.
What are you doing up this late?
Your teacher does not approve.
Mr. Nasujima!
Correct. It's been so long
since I heard your voice.
Hey, you know what?
Would you like to meet?
I'd love to see you.
We could catch up
on old times.
Where's Haruna?
Is she okay?
Don't worry,
she's standing right here.
She calls me "Mother" now.
Isn't that the sweetest thing?
Where are you?
Tokyo Hands.
You know where that is, right?
We're just strolling around,
so, if you have some time,
come by.
You'd better not
have hurt her!
I haven't laid a finger
on her... yet.
But, after tonight's party,
I'm going to give her
a nice, long, private lesson.
Let her go! Please!
Or, I'll--
A couple of your friends
are stopping by later.
Mikado and Masaomi.
[gasps]
Are you still...
close with them?
What have you done with them?
Nothing, yet. Promise.
But they'll be here soon enough.
[laughing]
[hangs up]
I love it. Shijima?
I want you to watch those boys
in the masks carefully.
Okay. What for?
If I know Anri
as well as I think,
she's going to call Mikado
in the next couple of minutes.
If he is under
one of those masks,
he'll be the one
whose phone starts ringing.
[Walker]
Come on, let's go,
let's go, let's go!
Is there an accident?
A red light? What?
Chill, dude. It's traffic.
What I wanna know is,
what the hell's causing it
this time of night?
[woman] At this hour,
traffic in Ikebukuro
is backed up
in all directions,
due to a series of accidents
in the area.
[horns honking]
There have been multiple
eyewitness reports
of reckless driving,
which the police
are now investigating...
Where's a cop
when you need one?
Goddamn bikers
with their goddamn horns.
Bet they're causing this.
[Kyohei]
There's a ton of 'em, too.
Perfect. That's all we need,
possessed bikers.
Hey, guys? Mikado and Masaomi
might be heading into the city.
I can call Masaomi.
Oh. Of course.
I'll call Mikado.
'Sup!
Hmm?
Who are you?
Just a friend
of some guys from Saitama,
whose bikes you torched.
You remember them, don't ya?
[gasps]
You alone?
Naw, I got tons of chicks!
Bet you don't get much action,
though. Too bad you--
Ha! Why don't you go find
a hole to die in, you dick?
[both laughing]
Yup. This town's
gone straight to hell.
You kids gotta be nuts,
walkin' around in a crowd,
smackin' people with bats.
Surprised no one stopped you,
or called the cops
on your asses yet.
Don't you all think
that's kinda weird?
[both whimper]
And do you all know
how much that hurt?
'Cause, if not,
you're about to find out!
[groaning]
What's wrong
with you bastards?
Don't you give a damn
what happens to Masaomi?
[Aoba]
Actually, no. We don't give
a damn what happens to him.
Huh?
[grunts]
We know all about
your little plan.
[phone ringing]
[gasps]
[another phone ringing]
[both phones ringing]
Anri's trying to call me.
[gasps]
I wonder what she wants
this late.
Hey there, Masaomi.
Mikado?
[ringing continues]
It feels like we haven't
seen each other in forever.
[Kururi]
I guess this chatroom's
over and done with.
[Mairu]
I'll miss it.
Oh, well.
The world's gotta
change with the times.
And you never know!
Someday, the world might need
this chatroom again!
Bring it back!
It might be ending,
but you know what?
I'm not too sad about it.
I'm glad it ended
with a big, fat bang.
Talk about entertaining!
Enjoy the end
of everything, people!
Bye-bye!
It was fun!
[Manami]
Sexy lab coat you got there.
Oh, hey.
I thought you took off.
I sort of wanted to pick
your brain some more
about Izaya.
[chuckles]
Stubborn, aren't you?
You're half-dead.
Where are you going?
[grunts, sighs]
To Celty Sturluson.
What?
I'm going out to find
the woman I love.
I know she's somewhere
out there in the city.
I can feel it.
I have to hurry, though,
because she probably has
her head back by now.
You sure? Maybe she
went back to Ireland.
I don't think she did.
Why not?
Because the sky's
the same color as her,
that's why.
I can't sit around
cooped up inside,
knowing Celty's somewhere,
up there, in that sky.
I envy you. I don't have
happy dreams like that anymore.
What I want
is simple, actually.
I want to keep on loving
the woman I love forever,
and to be with her, forever.
That's pretty much
all I want.
Of course, I want her
to be happy, too,
but... not if it gets
in the way of my happiness.
That sounds
like something a stalker,
or some wife-beating
scumbag would say.
I guess it does.
Believe me, I know what I'm
thinking about doing is harsh.
It'll be so much worse
than beating her up.
I hate that it has
to be this way.
But, still, I have
to go through with it.
Otherwise,
everything I've told her
up to this point will be a lie.
By now, she might have
her old memories back
and she might even kill me,
but I still have to do this.
[Anri] In his own way,
he is also taking a stand.
Mikado...
Is it really you?
Was that a question?
Sounded like one.
So, now, you get three answers
to choose from. Remember that?
[grunts]
And the three answers are:
One, Mikado Ryugamine!
Two, Mikado Ryugamine!
Three, Mikado Ryugamine!
I also remember
you totally ignored
my best joke that day.
Yeah, but even now,
on a scale from one to ten,
that joke scores a lame.
Or, the square root of three!
Wow, Mikado!
I can't believe
it's really you.
Well, of course it is!
Who'd you expect?
I just can't believe
you're here.
So, what happened?
You talk to Chikage?
Did he explain everything?
Not exactly.
Right now, he's probably
getting into a brawl
with Aoba and his guys.
I told them to take
their bats along with 'em,
but he's not gonna go down
that easy, is he?
Wait. You knew about us?
Sure. It was easy
to track you guys, too.
I just used the Dollars'
info network.
Hang on, man. If you knew
I was safe in the first place,
why'd you even bother
showing up?
It was a chance
to see you again.
And I also have something
I wanted to show you.
Sorry. Before I do,
I wanna tell you...
I'm the person
who started up the Dollars,
more or less.
Jeez, man!
It's about time
you came clean!
Yeah, but I promised Anri
I'd wait till the three of us
were together again
to talk about it.
Okay, then,
let's get Anri over here!
You said she
called you just now.
I don't wanna put her
in any danger, though.
What is it you wanted
to show me?
The last meeting
of the Dollars.
[Anri]
Both him...
...and him...
Whether they want to, or not,
their time has come
to take a stand and fight.
The city's time has come, too.
♪ [theme song playing]
[Masaomi] Here's a story
you probably heard before.
It's about a guy
and his best friend,
and the reunion one's been
dreaming about for a while.
Next time:
Life is an Unknown Course.
If you're not
into stories like this,
no one's forcing you
to watch.