♪ [singing in Japanese]
[grunting]
I want your Saika.
Name your price,
and I'll take her
off your hands.
My love, my love, my love,
my love, my love!
Aah! Aah!
[both shouting]
I always thought that
I could do anything for Saki!
♪ [singing resumes]
[Takashi]
Compared to the event
that's about to shake
this city to its core,
what's about to happen here
is trivial at best.
Do you want your gang
taken over or taken out?
What'll it be?
-What?
-You son of a--
You trying to pick
a fight with us?
My bad.
I guess if a strange dude
rolled up on me
asking what I just did,
I'd think he was some asshole
trying to pick a fight
with me, too.
You're right. That was
a risky move on your part.
Don't mad-dog me, bro.
Listen, you know Kadota?
From the Dollars?
Yeah. So?
A little while ago,
Kadota beat the piss out of me.
Afterwards, we made a deal
for me and my gang
to get out of Ikebukuro
and stay out.
Anyway, I heard
he got hit by a car.
I thought it was weird,
so I snooped around,
and then I found out you guys
are brawling with the Dollars.
I also heard that
before me and the Toramaru
showed up in 'Bukuro,
y'all were tearing
shit up here,
making it so folks were
afraid to go out at night.
I hear it got so bad,
Kadota and his peeps had
to squash y'all once before.
-You got beef with him--
-We didn't do shit to him,
-so get lost!
-Chill.
So you think we tried
to kill him, huh?
That's why you're here?
Yep. I sort of owe him one
for saving my girl Non.
I figure the least I can do
is find whoever hit him.
By the way, you know
about a group in the Dollars
that's trying
to clean up their ranks?
Word on the street is
they're the same dicks
that jumped my guys
last spring,
The same sons of bitches
that torched our bikes.
I get it now. You want
to use the Yellow Scarves
to smoke out the guys
that did that to you
and your gang.
You catch on quick.
I like that.
Now here's where
it gets confusing.
See, some of them used
to be in the Blue Squares,
and most of them
used to roll with y'all
in the Yellow Scarves.
And, to top that off,
the Yellow Scarves
took out the Blue Squares
back in the day.
[gasp]
I have no idea
what's going on.
I just want
to keep things simple.
That's why I'm here
all by my lonesome.
This don't involve
the rest of Toramaru.
So...
[gasp]
You and me are gonna settle this
the old-fashioned way.
If I beat you, what are we
gonna get out of it?
If you kick my ass,
I go to work for you
as your bodyguard.
My what?
Your bodyguard.
As in the guy
who's got your back
in your fight
with the Dollars.
Hell, even if I kick your ass,
I'm still going
after those guys,
so whatever, right?
Look, dude, you got, like,
a screw loose or something?
[laughing]
I get that a lot.
Why do we have to fight, though?
If you want to help us out,
just help us out.
I'd be down with that,
but you guys don't have
the best rep, know what I mean?
He really wants to do this.
[inhale]
Kick back for this one, guys.
[all gasp]
You got yourself a deal
and a fight.
-But, Chief--
-Hands and feet. No weapons.
I think I'm starting
to like you.
You dress like some kind
of wannabe player,
but your vibe is
straight-up old school.
I was about to say
the same thing, guy.
[Takashi]
Eh. Typical.
Whenever sub-intellectual
guys get together,
it always ends up in a fight.
If you'd decked Mikado
when you had the chance,
we wouldn't be here.
-Well, we're here.
-Yeah, too bad for you!
Yeah.
-Oh, crap.
-Thanks.
Damn it. I didn't even
see that com-- [gasp]
[yelling]
Son of a bitch,
that was close.
[Takashi]
Around the same time
that was happening,
three ladies, who couldn't
be more different,
were deep in conversation.
There you have it.
That should help explain
how you and I have
the same Saika.
Do you have any questions?
No, I don't.
I think I understand.
[Haruna]
Replication, huh?
If a thing like that's possible,
do you think you could
give me a sword, too?
I'm certain that transaction
would fall well beyond
your price range.
Besides,
if I used replication
to make more Saikas,
it would only lower
her value on the marketplace.
I'd like to avoid that.
Miss Sonohara.
Yes?
I was serious before
about my offer.
Will you sell
your Saika to me?
I didn't know I could.
And if I can, how would you
get her out of me?
If you really want to let go
of her, it is possible.
I'm prepared to pay
handsomely for her.
In the end, however,
the choice to sell her
is yours.
I don't know.
[man on TV]
Let's check in with Mr. Miyake
for breaking news
out of Ikebukuro.
Mr. Miyaki?
Uh, we're live here
at the scene
-outside Ikebukuro Station.
-Aw, you're kidding.
Look, can't you
take care of it?
I'm on lunch-- Oops.
...commuters made
a ghoulish discovery.
[Haruna]
Instead of selling her
to a total stranger,
give her to me.
I can cut Mikado and Masaomi
and have both of them eating
out of the palm of your hand.
No, you won't.
You shouldn't use Saika
to do that.
At least,
I think it's wrong.
If you cut someone you love,
they'll be different.
They're different because
their thoughts and feelings
aren't theirs anymore.
They're Saika's.
Well, that's not
how I see it,
but let's ask
the expert about it.
Is she right?
It all depends
on the situation.
For example,
you can cut someone
and not use Saika's power
to control them.
That person will continue
living their life
as they normally would,
never knowing Saika's curse.
If that's the scenario,
calling the person different
is blowing things
out of proportion.
Like beauty or intelligence,
you should consider
your power to wield Saika
a virtue, not a curse.
Ultimately, how you decide
to use your power
is entirely up to you.
Yeah, but a little while ago,
someone told me
I wasn't human anymore.
And if that's true,
then I don't think
I have the right to be
in love with anyone.
Really? Then what they said
applies to me as well.
Huh? I'm so sorry.
Th-That came out wrong.
Miss Sonohara,
let's just say
for argument's sake
you weren't human.
All you have to do
to become human again
is simply give up Saika,
because, in the end,
your blood and flesh
are human.
[Saika]
I love you.
I can't love you.
What is this? How scary.
Monster. Spare me. Save me.
No, no, no.
I'm scared. I'm scared.
I'm scared.
Did you see something?
[quivering]
Let me see if I understand
you correctly.
If one is not human,
they have no right to live,
love, or enjoy themselves?
Is that what you think?
Ms. Kujiragi, are you human?
Biologically speaking,
the answer is quite
convoluted, I'm afraid.
However, I can tell you how
I identify in human society.
Simply put, I am what is
referred to as a villain.
Eventually,
I will be exterminated
by someone seeking
justice or revenge.
Although I'm prepared
for that to happen,
I will try my best
to postpone it
and enjoy every moment
of my life until then.
-Miss Sonohara.
-Huh?
You are not even remotely
the same as I am.
Instead of sitting here
speaking with a villain
like myself,
you should be with
more wholesome company.
But I can't.
I leech off others
because I can't
survive on my own,
just like a parasite.
-And what's wrong with that?
-Huh?
If what you say is true
and there are people
who let you feed off them,
then it means they must be
benefitting somehow in return
for letting you do that.
That is not a parasitic
relationship.
It is symbiotic.
So there's no need to feel
indebted to them at all.
You see, no matter how much
Saika loves humanity,
in the end, she's a blade
that distorts
the human world.
There are two ways
to handle her.
You either control her
and make her your slave,
or you give yourself
completely over to her.
You're much too kind to do
either, Miss Sonohara.
You don't want to hurt anyone,
so you try to suppress Saika,
and, at the same time,
you can't bring yourself
to treat Saika as your slave.
You're trying so hard to find
a way to coexist with her,
but all you're doing
is painting yourself
into a corner.
You strike me as a good girl.
Good girls can't wield Saika.
[gasp]
[Haruna laughs]
You hear that, Anri?
This idiot's
totally asking for it.
She's expecting
someone with a grudge
to kill her.
What do you think?
Now's as good a time as any.
-[Anri sighs]
-Ms. Kujiragi,
If you hadn't sold
that Saika blade,
Anri's parents would
still be alive today.
-You're wrong.
-Huh?
If it weren't for Saika,
I wouldn't be sitting here.
-I wouldn't be here at all.
-[Haruna] What?
If it hadn't been for Saika,
my dad, he would've
killed me for sure.
I'm sorry, but I can't
give Saika up just yet.
She saved me.
I owe her my life
and I have to repay her.
I just-- I can't let her go
without doing that first.
Is that so?
Yes, and I promised my friends.
I promised to tell them
everything about me and Saika.
Until I can do that,
I have to keep on being
the same as I was.
I understand.
You can reach me there
if you change your mind.
Hold on. Aren't you going
to give me a card, too?
I have no potential
transactions with you,
Miss Niekawa.
Well, if you're going
to be rude...
What if I took your Saika?
What do you say to that?
Shall I electrocute you again?
[chuckle]
I don't know.
You want to find out
if you can?
No! Please stop it!
[Erika]
There you are, Anri!
I got some news
that's gonna make you--
Hey, what's in the--
No way!
You said they were
sold out of them!
Actually, they're mine.
Oh. Sorry about that.
Whoa. You're mega-hot.
You wouldn't happen to be
a fellow layer, would you?
Do you mean cosplayer?
I'm interested in it,
but I've never tried it.
Then today's your lucky day.
I have a cosplay club.
If you're a friend of Anri's,
you're more
than welcome to join.
-No, I don't--
-You're gonna love it.
We got around 270 different
kinds of costumes to try.
Shrine maidens,
fallen angels, sexy maids.
You name it, we got it.
Do you have Gothic
Lolita outfits?
That's my number.
But you can expect a call
from me in the very near future.
What a boring day.
I think I'll head home now.
But you can expect
to see me again soon.
Your hot friend didn't seem
like she was all that
into cosplay.
I hope I didn't
make her feel weird.
Not at all. And thanks.
You came just in time.
-Uh, sure.
-What's up?
You said you had some news?
Oh right, that.
Guess what, guess what!
Dotachin woke up
from his coma.
He's awake, and we can
go see him tomorrow.
Can you believe it?
He's gonna be okay.
[thinking] Shit. If he lands
one of those, I'm so dead.
Hyuh!
[Yellow Scarves chatter]
-Yeah!
-Now you got him!
[onlookers gasp]
He's crazy.
[coughing]
Dude, if you're
dumb enough to grab me,
you might as well
hang on for the ride!
[boy]
What do you want,
old man?
[laughing]
They say you can always
find the dumbest guys
in the highest places.
And here you dumb-asses are.
[indistinct chatter]
Oh, shit, it's Izumii.
Hey!
I'm coming back up,
so don't go anywhere,
got it?
It's time for a pop quiz.
Can anyone tell me the name
of the chickenshit bastard
who abandoned Saki Mikajima
after I broke her legs?
-[laughing]
-[growls]
-Izumii!
-Wait.
That's Mr. Izumii to you.
Raah!
[grunting]
[chuckling]
[grunt]
[Takashi] Yep. Whenever
punks like this get together,
the blood always flows.
Over on this side of town,
we have a man who's decided
against using his
unbelievable strength.
[man]
Hey.
You're the guy
who likes to swing
sign posts around.
I bet if you wanted to,
you could snap these bars
in half, couldn't you?
-Wrong guy, pal.
-Come on.
The glasses,
the bartender getup...
It's you.
On second thought,
maybe it's good
you don't try anything
like breaking out.
I don't know if you know,
but right now
this place is surrounded
by reporters.
Oh, yeah? Why?
The city's got
a bug up its ass
about some chick's head they
found in front of the station.
You want to know
something else?
Here's what I heard:
the head's still alive.
Folks say it might be
the Headless Rider's head.
And they're bringing it here
for safekeeping.
Is that so?
Dude, I know
you're one of that
demon sword's zombies.
What? I don't know
what you're talking--
Don't you friggin' lie to me!
It's kind of perfect
you're in here,
knowing what you know
and telling me.
You think I wouldn't
get suspicious?
You think I'm stupid
or something?
[chuckling] Okay, okay,
you got me. My bad.
You're right.
The only reason I'm here
is 'cause Mother
told me to see you.
So what's your angle?
Why'd you tell me
about that head?
I was hoping
you'd tear the place up
the next time they took you
out for interrogation.
While you did, the plan was for
someone else to grab the head.
I don't see the point.
You guys on Celty's side?
Or do you got something in mind
you want to use her for?
Neither, actually. But get this.
If you say you're in,
I could make that
assault charge against you
-disappear like--
-Shizuo Heiwajima, you can go.
[Shizuo]
What?
[chatter]
What the hell's going on?
[Takashi]
They said the woman
who accused him
confessed that he
never touched her.
Needless to say, the charges
against him were dropped.
[crowd gasping, murmuring]
[woman]
There was a huge explosion
in front of the police station!
The squad car
carrying the head
is completely
engulfed in flames.
[Shizuo]
Hey.
Varona. It's you, isn't it?
[police whistles blow]
It was her back then,
and I bet you've got something
to do with this, too,
don't you, Izaya?
[Takashi]
A little while
before that happened...
Haruna.
Oh, hi, Dad. What's up?
Where have you been
all this time?
I was so worried.
How did you know
where to find me?
The Dollars told me
you were at Raira Hospital.
I tailed you from there.
Really, Dad,
getting help from a gang?
Would you stop it?
I said I was worried about--
Shut your mouth already.
Right. Sure.
Go on home, Dad,
and forget you saw me here.
[grunt]
What did you--
[chuckle]
Hmm.
[humming]
Ooh. Your daughter's
a fine woman
when she's not talking.
Anyway, if Saika's child
and her child's child
slash each other,
no matter how long
one's been possessed
or how strong the other is,
the one who gets slashed last
controls the other.
Haruna,
you didn't know that.
No, I bet you thought
you're the only child of Saika
who's ever overcome
the original.
Oh, and in case
you're wondering
what would happen
if one child slashed another,
that remains to be seen.
[gasp]
Either way,
as long as I can use Saika
to control you, Haruna...
you can be sure
I'll smother you with love.
Yeah. I'm gonna love
that body of yours to pieces.
[laughing]
[footsteps]
-[voice] I am--
-Huh?
Cel... Cel... ty.
Celty. Celty.
I am Celty.
You okay? Wowsers.
That must've been
some nightmare.
Where's my head?
What happened to my head?
Oh, don't worry.
[chuckle]
There's this crazy rumor
about your head being fake
that's making
the rounds online.
Walker and I whipped it up
last night and set it loose.
Oh. I have to do something.
If someone decides
to cremate it, then I--
I'll be--
I know.
I'll figure something out.
Sorry for freaking out
like that.
I'm okay now.
That's good.
Actually,
Seiji sorta freaked out
even worse than you did.
He threatened to storm
the police station,
so my Dad shot him
full of sedatives.
Namie saw what we did
to Seiji, lost it,
and then I had
to knock her out, too.
We tucked her in
right next to her brother.
-[laughter]
-[doorbell rings]
Now what?
[knocking]
Oh, Shinra,
a young lady with glasses
just showed up,
and she's wondering if you
can spare a minute for her.
Glasses?
Oh, that's got to be Anri.
You can send her in.
Since she's here,
maybe we should tell her
about Mikado.
Yeah. I don't know. Uh--
Uh...
Who are you?
I'm pleased to meet you.
My name is Kasane Kujiragi.
♪ [singing in Japanese]
[Varona]
For what reason am I here?
Why did I accept job?
What is it about foreign city
that scare me?
What is reason
for why I have changed?
Next time: Lost in Dark.