["Day You Laugh"
by Toyonaga Toshiyuki]
♪ ♪
[man singing in Japanese]
‐ He made me scream out
each note
as he carved 'em
into my arm.
‐ Here's what I know
about you.
You have two sisters.
Kururi and Mairu, right?
‐ Who's Nakura?
HARUYA: Eh, it's this guy
who's been playing head games
with the boss' daughter.
MAN: [on phone with distorted
voice] Question one,
what do Chikage,
Amphisbaena,
and Mr. Kumoi of Heaven's Slave
have in common?
[man singing in Japanese]
♪ ♪
KASANE: Thank you for taking
time out of your busy day
to speak with me,
Mr. Nakura.
NAKURA: Oh, sure,
Ms. Kujiragi. Happy to.
I don't need an insurance policy
or anything, through.
‐ Actually,
the reason I'm here
is to find out
about Izaya Orihara.
Do you know him?
NAKURA: Oh, yeah.
No way am I gonna forget someone
with a weird name like that.
We were in middle school.
He in trouble?
Wait, he's not using my name
again, is he?
‐ Again?
NAKURA:
Yeah, funny story.
I sold him my name,
believe it or not.
‐ I'm sorry, you what?
‐ He wanted to buy
something online,
but he didn't want
to use his name,
so he asked if he could
use mine instead.
It's not like it's
my bank account or anything,
so I sold it to him.
After that, I started getting
all these packages in the mail.
‐ What was in these packages?
NAKURA: Just books‐‐
stuff about folklore mostly
and some weird ones.
Nothing special, really.
‐ And do you remember
what he was like in school?
NAKURA: I don't remember
seeing him much in class,
but I used to see him
with this nerdy guy
with glasses
and a white lab coat.
‐ And do you remember his name?
NAKURA: Uh‐uh.
So, why do you want to know
about Orihara?
You never said.
‐ I'm afraid I can't really
go into detail about that.
I can tell you
that his name popped up
on a list of beneficiaries
that my company handles.
NAKURA: Really? Huh.
So you think
it's insurance fraud then.
Yeah, that sounds like something
Orihara'd be into.
Oh, I just remembered.
One time he told me
observing humans
was a hobby of his.
‐ Observing humans?
Really?
‐ I know, weird, huh?
And he didn't say it
like he was being
condescending about it either.
More like‐‐you know cat lovers,
when they see a cat,
it could be pissed off
or whatever,
they see it and go,
"Oh, look, isn't that sweet"?
‐ But if he sees other humans
as nothing more than cats,
that is condescending.
‐ Sure, if we're talking
about someone normal,
but with him, he sees a cat get
hit by a car or sick and dying
with its throat ripped out
by another cat,
he doesn't see it
as a horrible thing.
He'd go, "How sweet,"
just like that.
‐ Please, officer,
can't we talk about this?
‐ Nope.
If you want to talk about it,
you might want to call
your lawyer.
‐ But I checked
the traffic laws in Tokyo,
and, with all due respect,
officer, sir,
light vehicles and horses
don't have to have headlights.
It's under Headlight
Requirements, see?
"Cattle and horses excepted."
‐ Crap, she got us.
‐ What? What'd you say?
You admit it?
You dirty, no‐good, fascist cop,
how dare you?
‐ Right. Then you're
sticking to your story
that your vehicle's a horse?
‐ At last you get it.
‐ And you admit
you've been riding
this light vehicle
you call a horse
like a motorcycle
on city streets, yeah?
‐ Huh?
‐ Can you tell me
the one traffic regulation
that all vehicles‐‐
light or otherwise‐‐
must obey?
‐ Uh, well‐‐
‐ The posted speed limit.
Even bicycles have to obey
that one.
Now then, would you say
you were exceeding it
when you refused
to pull over?
‐ [gasps, sobs]
‐ I had to chase you
for five minutes before you did,
hotshot.
Anyway, I'll need to see
your license and regi‐‐
[Cóiste‐Bodhar neighs]
Goddamn it, halt!
[energetic music]
[sirens wailing]
[grumbles]
‐ [squeals]
♪ ♪
‐ Jeez.
I almost didn't make it home
today.
‐ What's wrong, Celty?
I can't stand seeing you sad,
'cause that makes me sad.
It's the kind of sad I can feel
right down to my bones,
the kind of sad‐‐
[coughs]
No, it's okay.
[groans]
See? I'm fine now.
I just got a little saliva
down my windpipe is all.
‐ Oh, good,
you had me worried.
I shouldn't barge in when you're
trying to rest. I'm sorry.
‐ You don't have to apologize
to me.
I should be the one apologizing
for not getting up
and holding you in my arms.
I can't stand this.
‐ You're so sweet.
‐ The past couple of days,
hearing your stories
about where you've been
and what's going on outside
have meant so much.
Believe it or not,
it helps ease my pain.
I guess, in a way,
keeping my spirits up's
helped my better
than any medicine could.
It sounds New Agey,
but the fact is,
you're the best medicine for me.
‐ Thank you.
‐ Maybe I deserved it.
‐ What do you mean, this?
‐ You know, how I treated Izaya
when he was in the hospital.
I kind of blew him off, and that
was a mean thing for me to do.
‐ Oh, don't even go there.
Whatever happened to him
was his fault.
He pissed off
so many people,
it was bound to happen to him
at some point.
‐ Yeah, I know,
but I've known him
since our junior high days,
and we've been friends
since then.
‐ [blows whistle]
Was he a dirtbag
back then too?
‐ Well, when I met him
he didn't really socialize
with anyone else in class.
He was kind of a loner.
Come to think of it,
I doubt he's ever had anyone
he could open up to.
‐ With his personality,
I doubt he ever will.
Now, let's change
your bandages.
‐ Ooh, ooh!
[laughs]
The thought of you
looking at my wounds
is both embarrassing
and kinky.
I don't know
if I can take it.
What do I do? What do I do?
I'm all goose‐pimply.
‐ Please behave.
I always wondered
where you got that scar.
I remember you telling me
about a fight
you got dragged into once.
Is it from that?
‐ Uh‐huh.
Someone stabbed me with a knife.
‐ A knife? You never told me
you were stabbed!
I always thought
you got it
because you got pushed
down some stairs.
How could you not tell me?
‐ I thought I did.
No, on second thought,
you know what, you're right.
I guess I never told you
how I got this thing.
Even now,
after all these years,
I still have mixed feelings
about it.
[bell ringing]
It goes all the way back
to 12 years ago.
I met him on the first day
of school.
Excuse me, do you want to join
the biology club?
I mean,
you want to start one?
[voiceover]
Izaya Orihara.
‐ Sorry, not interested.
‐ Oh, you don't have to be
interested.
Just help set it up.
It'll be fun.
‐ Your name's Kishitani, right?
‐ Call me Shinra.
You're‐‐
sorry, hey,
what's your name again?
‐ Izaya Orihara.
‐ Oh, yeah, that's right.
Orihara, huh?
Like I said,
call me Shinra.
Can I call you Izaya?
‐ Why would you want me to help
start a biology club with you
when you don't even know
who I am?
‐ Well, didn't you hear
what the teacher just said?
To start a club here you need
two or more people to do it.
‐ Yeah, I get that,
but why me?
‐ 'Cause you like observing
living creatures, that's why.
‐ Huh?
‐ Remember,
when you introduced yourself?
You told the class you like
to observe all kinds of people.
‐ So what does that have to do
with a biology club?
‐ Aren't humans
living creatures?
‐ Uh‐‐whatever. I still don't
want to start a stupid club.
‐ All right then.
If you say so.
But I'm gonna ask you again
tomorrow.
‐ Don't bother.
My answer tomorrow's gonna be
the same as it is today.
‐ Then how about the day after?
‐ Same answer.
‐ Come on, please?
I'll let you be the president.
‐ I don't care about being
president of your club.
Why don't you go ask
someone else, like‐‐
I don't know,
one of your friends
from grade school
or something.
‐ Do I look like I have friends?
Yes or no.
[children laughing]
‐ Well, since you put it
that way, no, you don't.
‐ Wrong answer!
‐ [groans]
‐ I have one friend.
‐ Huh?
‐ He's at a different school
though,
so he doesn't count.
Maybe I'll make some here.
‐ Sorry to be the one
to break this to you,
but I highly doubt that.
I'm sure if you look
hard enough,
you'll find someone else
who's into biology junk.
‐ Yeah, maybe, I guess,
but if I find someone
and they really like biology,
that's not gonna work for me.
I don't want to have to do
projects all the time,
know what I mean?
‐ I'm confused.
Do you like biology
or don't you?
‐ Well, if you want
to know the truth,
I don't even want to be
in a club.
The girl I love,
she said, "Shinra,
"you don't have any friends.
Why don't you join a club?"
And here we are.
[laughs]
Anyway, you'd be perfect
for the club.
I don't care that you're
not into it.
In fact,
I like that about you.
Please? We'll have fun
looking for Tsuchinokos.
‐ No thanks. Biology clubs
don't do that anyway.
NAKURA: [voiceover] So Izaya
blew me off and walked away.
I thought that was
the end of that.
But then he started
asking around about me.
I guess he found me amusing
because we were so different.
Unlike him, I didn't seem
interested in people much.
I guess he was curious about how
someone like me looked at life.
‐ About the club, if I can be
vice president, then I'm in.
‐ Oh! Oh, thank you!
[voiceover]
I was so happy.
That was the start
of the Raijin Junior High
Biology Club.
Then, during our summer break‐‐
SHINRA: I'm expecting
great things from you,
Vice President.
‐ So what you're saying is,
you're not gonna do a thing,
Mr. President?
‐ No, not exactly.
I'll be cheering you on.
We're officially
a two‐member club.
That means you can come up
with your own activities.
What do you say?
‐ 'Kay, then.
If you die here, I propose
to observe how your corpse rots,
then exhibit it
at the cultural festival.
Right. American universities
have research facilities
where they do
that kind of stuff.
They call them body farms.
Pretty creepy, huh?
‐ How do you know that?
‐ My dad does research
for a pharmaceutical company
there.
He tells me all kinds
of cool trivia like that.
I just thought of something.
What are you gonna do
if my body doesn't decompose?
‐ Huh?
‐ Let's suppose you have
a female corpse‐‐
a gorgeous female corpse
with her heart intact,
and say her corpse
doesn't rot.
People would just see
a beautiful corpse,
but what if you saw her
as the love of your life?
And what if you want to find out
how she feels about you?
I mean, she's a corpse.
‐ Well, if you're crazy enough,
I guess you can
fake talking to her
with ventriloquism.
‐ Let's say
this beautiful woman's corpse
that doesn't rot
can also walk around?
In other words,
it went from being
a non‐decomposing corpse
to a non‐decomposing zombie.
If you could talk to her,
do you think
it would be possible
to fall in love with her?
‐ Are you serious?
‐ Suppose all the zombie's
internals are fine,
just the heart stopped,
and suppose you could talk
and joke around with her?
What would that be like?
‐ I guess it'd be the same
as talking to a person
without a heartbeat
and a funny way of walking.
‐ Then it wouldn't be weird
to fall in love
with that zombie, would it?
I mean, if it's normal
to love a human
but abnormal to love a zombie,
what do you do then?
Where do you draw the line?
‐ Well, I don't think
it really matters
who you fall in love with.
It's cool as long as
you don't hurt anyone, right?
‐ Uh‐uhh.
I'd gladly hurt someone,
'cause I love her.
‐ Wow. Seriously?
‐ You know it!
Even back then I loved you
as much as‐‐
[bones cracking]
[groans] Ow.
Without you...
‐ Take it easy,
don't get excited.
‐ Life is just a big, black...
‐ Okay, I get it, I get it.
Easy, it's okay.
‐ Icky hole of despair.
Guess I overdid it.
Sorry for spazzing out.
‐ It's fine,
please just stay in bed.
‐ The next month was
when it happened.
[baseball announcements]
SHINRA: Oh, come on,
we talked about this.
You were gonna stop taking bets
on baseball games.
‐ Stop nagging me.
It's none of your business
anyway.
‐ Actually, it is my business,
'cause I already told my family
you're my friend.
‐ So what?
‐ So if you're doing
something illegal at school
and I don't say
something about it,
that's not right.
‐ Shinra, are you an idiot?
'Cause right now it sounds like
you can't make a decision
without worrying
about what other people think.
You're like a puppet.
‐ But if that person is
someone I love,
I wouldn't mind being
their puppet at all.
‐ You're hopeless,
you know that?
[dramatic music]
‐ [groans]
MAN: Kishitani, what happened?
‐ I guess I got stabbed.
Would you call an ambulance,
please?
[siren wailing]
NAKURA:
[voiceover] A few hours later,
Izaya surrendered to the police
and was taken into custody.
We didn't press charges though,
and it was over
before too many people
found out about it.
♪ ♪
‐ Wait, it was Izaya?
Are you telling me
Izaya stabbed you?
All right, now I'm mad‐‐
really mad!
‐ No, calm down, Celty.
‐ I'll make that rotten,
no‐good‐‐
‐ It's not like that?
‐ Huh?
‐ It‐‐that's not what happened.
‐ Well, then what did happen?
‐ [groans]
♪ ♪
[breathes deeply]
‐ Now you're sleeping?
[phone ringing]
‐ Hi, Nakura. Nice work.
You're a good actor.
‐ Huh?
Wait, were you listening in?
IZAYA: Yep,
I heard every single lie.
NAKURA: What did you
get me into?
That lady's
no insurance agent.
Is she Yakuza?
Look, I don't want
anything to do with that stuff,
ever.
‐ Oh, my. Someone's honed
their observation skills.
You're right, she's not
an insurance agent,
nor does she work for one.
Her name really is
Kasane Kujiragi though.
And don't worry
about the Yakuza.
This is different.
NAKURA: A‐are you sure
about that?
IZAYA: Super sure,
although you almost had
the Awakusu coming after you
for two different reasons.
‐ What?
IZAYA: Remember that thing
we started our senior year
of high school, Amphisbaena?
‐ Oh, that thing?
Yeah, I do.
It was just a bigger version
of our betting pool
for baseball.
IZAYA: That's the one.
I believe you
called yourself Tokage.
‐ Right, but it was only around
for a little while.
IZAYA: Well, do you remember
a girl back then
whose nickname was Mimizu?
‐ No. I don't.
IZAYA: I don't either.
In fact,
I've never heard of her.
Anyway,
she took over Amphisbaena
and she's been doing business
with it on the Awakusu's turf.
‐ Huh?
IZAYA:
Oh, you should've heard her.
She was going on and on,
"the boss" this
and "the boss" that.
She worshipped you.
I guess she thought
she was your lover,
and she made everyone
think that too,
even though you're not
the boss anymore.
NAKURA: All right,
what's the deal?
Where's this going?
‐ Don't worry.
Everything's been
taken care of.
Oh, do you want to know
what's even funnier?
She was locking horns
with Shijima.
Can you beat that?
NAKURA: What?
‐ [laughs]
NAKURA: You mean
the guy who started
that underground drug club?
‐ That's right,
rich boy Shijima.
I never met him back then,
but you did,
and if memory serves,
you co‐founded the club with him
and called yourself Kumoi.
Well, now he's moved up
to making harder drugs,
'cause that's what
Mr. Kumoi wants.
NAKURA: Wait, hold on!
IZAYA: It's funny.
‐ You're kidding!
IZAYA: Nope,
Shijima calls himself
"the second in command,"
and get this,
he keeps his people in line
by hurting himself and saying
Kumoi did it to punish him.
This Kumoi sure sounds
like a bastard, huh?
‐ [panting] This is crazy.
I can't get involved with this!
What am I gonna do?
IZAYA: Calm down.
You don't have to worry
about Shijima.
‐ For real?
IZAYA: Sure.
You don't have anything to worry
about from anyone,
and if things do go south,
you can always have Shinra
change your face again.
NAKURA: [sobbing] But I‐‐
I gotta‐‐what am I gonna do?
‐ Nothing. Hey, if you
don't like where you're at now,
complain to your past self
about it.
Okay, then, talk to you later.
Bye.
NAKURA: [whimpering]
Why?
Why's this happening to me?
Shit. Shit. Shit! Shit!
‐ I wouldn't mind being
their puppet at all.
‐ You're hopeless,
you know that?
NAKURA: Orihara.
‐ Hey. What's up, Nakura?
Sorry, betting's closed
for today.
‐ I know. Listen, man,
that bet I made yesterday, I‐‐
I want to cancel it,
I need the cash back.
I need it now,
before my dad finds out
I took it from his wallet.
He'll kick my ass!
‐ That's your problem,
not mine.
I never forced you to place
any bets, that was all you.
NAKURA: [whimpering]
‐ Oh, Nakura.
Drop the knife, man.
‐ Shut up.
I want my money back!
Come on! Give it to me!
IZAYA: Not gonna happen.
Giving you your cash back
won't do me any favors.
I know you.
When someone wins,
you're there,
asking for a handout.
We've gotten complaints.
‐ No. It's a lie.
Give me back my money!
‐ You're such a moron.
‐ No! [grunts]
[wincing]
‐ [whimpers]
SHINRA: [wincing]
NAKURA: No. No, no.
No. I‐I was just trying
to scare Orihara. I was‐‐
‐ [wincing]
‐ I didn't‐‐I didn't!
No! No!
‐ Hang on.
I'll call an ambulance.
‐ No, wait. Duct tape.
I gotta stop‐‐stop
the bleeding first.
[chuckles]
I guess I'm not much of a hero,
huh?
I was hoping to impress someone
with my bravery.
[groans]
‐ Don't talk.
‐ No, I'm fine.
He didn't hit
any internal organs.
[groaning]
‐ Hey, Shinra, I have an idea.
Do you mind if we play this
as if I stabbed you?
‐ Why?
‐ Yes or no.
And if you say yes,
I'll spend my life
making Nakura regret it.
‐ So, what did you tell him?
‐ Um, "Go ahead," I guess.
‐ I knew you could be ruthless
from time to time,
but that was ruthless.
‐ [chuckles]
I play the straight arrow
'cause I know it turns you on.
‐ Who knew Izaya would
deal justice like that?
‐ He and I are different,
but we're both
full of surprises.
[chuckles]
Maybe he did it
because he thought
it would be fun.
‐ On this latest job, he had me
get some gambling chips,
let someone steal
a laptop off me...
[cell doors slamming shut]
And keep his little sister safe.
[all groaning]
‐ Just in time.
Thank you.
‐ If you want to thank someone,
thank your brother.
‐ No way, really?
[phone ringing]
‐ Hey, you okay?
I just got jumped
by these goons,
but Master Eijirou came
in the nick of time
and beat 'em all to mush.
[Cóiste‐Bodhar neighs]
So what about you?
Did you get attacked too?
CELTY: My opinion about you
changed today.
You worry about your family,
just like any normal person
would.
‐ I don't know about that.
The harder you try to see
the good in people,
the easier it is
to fake you out.
‐ Thanks.
Now what about the name?
‐ Right. Although it might be
a bit hard to believe‐‐
‐ Just tell me.
‐ [chuckles]
Jinnai Yodogiri.
He's the mastermind who had
that stalker attack Shinra.
Or maybe he's playing
the mastermind, who knows?
‐ And where is he now?
‐ I'm tracking him.
And if I do find him,
it's gonna cost you extra.
‐ Hey.
‐ Hmm?
‐ No, never mind.
[Cóiste‐Bodhar neighs]
IZAYA: [voiceover]
You're wrong, transporter.
I asked you to protect
my sisters
because I didn't want them
to come to the bar
where Haruna Niekawa was.
That's all there is to that.
[phone ringing]
Oh, well, the transporter
didn't ask for it.
I'm pretty sure she knew
it was here though.
‐ Just when I thought
you couldn't get any lower.
As much as I hate
The Headless Rider,
what you're doing is wrong.
I think I'm starting
to feel sorry for her.
I mean, technically speaking,
her head seduced Seiji,
not the rest of her.
‐ Yes, well,
I knew she wouldn't demand
I hand it over,
which is good, because I wanted
to see if there'd be any...
change to it.
Nope, it looks the same.
‐ I'm sure I felt it back there.
[footsteps]
I knew it.
He's got my head.
Why though?
You'll never change, Izaya.
I can't trust you.
MAIRU: Look, there he is!
Wait up, Izaya!
‐ Hmm?
‐ Izaya!
‐ Hey! [laughs]
‐ Hey, guys,
thanks for calling out
before trying to kick me
in the head.
‐ That's 'cause I don't think
you're a butt hole anymore.
I hear that you asked
The Headless Rider
to protect Kururi.
Is that for real, or what?
‐ Did you really?
‐ Oh, I had something
I didn't want The Headless Rider
knowing about.
If you want to know the truth,
I used you as a decoy.
‐ Whatever, that's cool.
Thanks, Izaya.
‐ Thanks a lot.
‐ [chuckles]
After all these years,
I still can't figure you out.
MAIRU: Well, maybe you would
if you weren't so darn crooked.
KURURI: And stubborn.
["Never Say Never"
by Three Lights Down Kings]
[man singing in Japanese]
♪ ♪