["Headhunt" by Okamoto's]
[man singing in Japanese]
♪ ♪
‐ It's time to die.
SHIKI: Some of my
younger associates
got roughed up
pretty bad near there.
MASAOMI: The Dollars
are in danger.
At least, I've got the feeling
that they are.
MIKADO: The Dollars?
CHIKAGE: An eye for an eye.
A tooth for a tooth.
AKANE: You won't get away.
VARONA: Play time
for children is over.
[tires squeal]
♪ ♪
CELTY: I couldn't understand
exactly what had happened.
All I knew was that someone
had done something to me.
That's all that was important.
[jazzy bass music]
♪ ♪
As I lay there
in a haze of delayed pain,
only trivial thoughts
came to mind...
[computer beeps]
Like last night's chat session
and the conversation
Shinra and I had
before I left...
‐ What kind of job?
♪ ♪
CELTY: And thoughts
about Shinra...
‐ Give me a kiss!
CELTY: And more thoughts
about Shinra.
[crunch]
‐ Ow, ow, ow, ow, ow!
Ow, ow, ow!
Ow, ow, ow, ow!
♪ ♪
‐ Oh.
‐ Did you see that?
[indistinct chatter]
MAN: Did you get
the license plate number?
♪ ♪
[jazzy bass music]
‐ [groans]
I really wish that Celty
would hurry up
and come back already.
[groans]
[doorbell rings]
Coming!
Celty, I'm glad you're back!
I was just thinking about you.
Don't tell me
you forgot your key‐‐
‐ [grunts]
SHINRA: What is it now?
If this is about
that wounded guy you‐‐
[grunts]
SHIZUO: I know.
He's still in town.
‐ Huh?
[quietly] Who's that?
‐ [exhales sharply]
‐ [whimpers softly]
‐ Uh...
[exhales]
[gasps]
Did you kidnap a kid?
‐ [growls]
‐ [sighs]
We didn't kidnap anyone.
‐ [grunts]
SHINRA: Well,
if you're looking for Celty,
she's out on a job
for Mr. Shiki.
Though to be perfectly honest
with you,
I don't think
she's been all that keen
on accepting jobs
from them lately.
I hear they're all busy
trying to figure out
if the Medei Group
will ally with the Asuki Group.
Who knows what's going on?
In any case, it isn't even
like Celty has to work.
I wonder what kind
of stay‐at‐home wife she'd make?
What the‐‐
for some reason,
I just pictured myself
as a stay‐at‐home husband.
Whoa, shake it off, Shinra.
Think of Celty
in a maid's apron.
[moans]
Oh, yeah.
‐ He's perverted all right.
SHINRA: Now I'm picturing
me in an apron.
‐ [sighs]
SHINRA: Why does this
keep happening?
AKANE: [crying]
SHINRA: Well, I guess
if she's going
to wear an apron for me,
than I'd be fine...
‐ [clears throat]
‐ Perhaps we should
get back to business.
This is Jinnai Yodogiri.
You may not recognize his face,
but he's been
in the news lately,
so you've probably heard of him.
He ran the Yodogiri
Shining Corporation.
CELTY: Oh, Ruri Hijiribe's
last agency.
SHIKI: It's not widely known,
but we also had dealings
with the agency.
The thing is, we had what you
might consider a falling out.
CELTY: With a talent agency
president?
‐ Former.
He's gone now.
Yodogiri seems
to have disappeared.
If you come across
any information,
I'd appreciate
you contacting us.
CELTY: I'm just a transporter,
so I don't know
if I'll be much use
with something like
a missing person.
‐ Yes, of course.
I know.
This is just something
I'd like you to keep in mind.
The real job I have
for you today is something else,
Although, this one's also
a bit of a stretch
for a transporter.
This is Akane Awakusu.
She's the granddaughter
of our president.
I'd like you to assist us
in locating her
and providing some protection.
The fact is,
she's run away from home.
Apparently,
the kind of business we run
doesn't sit well with her.
CELTY: It doesn't sit
too well with me either.
‐ Hmm.
SLOAN: Is too much.
I can't take anymore.
It's so distracting.
I can't walk.
No!
‐ If you will uncover eyes,
Sloan,
you'll see you are sitting.
Seated people
don't need to be walking.
SLOAN: It's all
my mind can think of.
On the street just now,
that sukiyaki shop...
WOMAN: Somebody stop him
before he gets away!
‐ And place for shabu‐shabu...
[cow moos]
All I can think about is beef.
How?
How is that cows
can eat nothing but trash
yet grow to such large sizes?
‐ They have specific
microscopic organisms
living inside stomachs
that react with the grass
in conjunction with cow saliva.
It produces amino acids,
which cow absorbs.
Ergo, massive bovine growth.
Is no mystery.
‐ So that's how cow's do it.
I knew you'd have answer,
Varona.
Now I can eat
all the steak I want
without worry about
that question nagging at me.
My curiosity now satisfied.
I'm going to drink milk too.
Even though is little strange
for humans to drink milk of cow.
Wait.
Hold on.
What?
Is no good.
Now is bothering me too much.
Speaking of milk,
why do guys have nipples?
Puzzle of male nipple
must be solved.
Until then, I do not move
from this spot!
‐ During fetal stage
is span of time
when embryo sex
is not determined.
Nipples get formed well before
that particular verdict is in.
‐ Oh, oh, is amazing!
Your logic is flawless.
[door opens]
BOTH: Hmm?
‐ Thank you both for coming.
I imagine that
you must be busy people,
so I do apologize
for keeping you waiting.
Now then,
I'm afraid that I have
precious little time myself,
so you'll forgive me
if I get right to the point.
There's a task
I'd like you to perform for me.
It should be simple enough.
You see, I need you to locate
a particular young lady
and kidnap her.
I know it seems strange
asking assassins
such as yourselves
to abduct a child...
[chuckles]
I realize the contract
is somewhat bizarre.
There are yakuza in this city.
I guess you'd call them
the mafia of Japan.
[chuckles]
This girl's the granddaughter
of one of the local bosses,
and what I'd like you
to do is capture her,
preferably alive
if at all possible.
‐ Understood,
but outcome you desire
may cost extra.
We can do kidnapping
without anyone seeing our faces,
but if we get
on yakuza's bad side,
we must be compensated.
‐ Yes, yes.
Of course.
The thing is, my sources say
the situation is escalating.
There's speculation that
the members
of her grandfather's gang
might hire a bodyguard
who could cause trouble for you.
Although it strikes me
as somewhat hard to believe.
‐ Is guard really
that formidable?
Just yes or no.
I require prompt answer, please.
‐ Well, to be honest with you,
the issue isn't
whether the person in question
is weak or strong.
This guard's
something of a magician.
‐ What you mean?
‐ As luck would have it,
a video of this person
was recently posted online.
I believe
it would be more expedient
for you to see
what I'm talking about
for yourselves.
It's called the Black Rider...
[Cóiste‐Bodhar neighs]
And it's something
of an urban legend.
I can't imagine
how these tricks are being done.
[soft dramatic music]
CELTY: What should I do?
Head home for now
and tell Shinra or...
♪ ♪
[sighs] I should probably
start searching
before night falls.
[Cóiste‐Bodhar neighs]
As I began to search,
I never dreamed
that the very girl
I was hired to find
happened to be at our apartment.
Not to mention...
‐ [speaks Japanese]
One question:
if I would kill
this Black Rider,
is that something
you would allow?
‐ Hmm, thanks
for explaining things.
Your name was Tom, right?
I think it's all
pretty much cleared up now.
So what did you
kidnap the girl for?
[metal screeches]
[grunts]
SHIZUO: [grunts, exhales]
‐ [groans]
‐ Sorry about that.
I'll pay for it.
SHINRA: It's okay.
I was just thinking
I could use a new one.
‐ Actually,
I feel bad for the people
who spent their time
making this cup.
SHINRA: Sure,
but I'm wondering
if you feel the same kind
of humility and remorse
for all those road signs
and guard rails you destroyed.
Well, got that off my chest.
I'm sorry.
Anyway, I knew you didn't
kidnap the girl,
because why would you?
When all you'd have to do is
rip open a bank vault
with your bare hands.
‐ [growls]
TOM: Easy.
We do have a kid here.
SHINRA: It's okay.
You can relax now.
I'm Shinra Kishitani.
Would you mind
telling me your name?
AKANE: [coughs]
BOTH: Hmm?
‐ [coughs]
‐ Oh.
[gasps]
Hey, there's a guest futon
in the next room.
Get it ready.
Quick.
SHIZUO: Hmm?
‐ Hurry.
She's got a fever.
AKANE: [coughing]
‐ [grunts]
[soft piano music]
‐ [grunts, exhales]
♪ ♪
BOY: Hey.
Since debating the choices
isn't getting us anywhere,
why don't we bring this
to a vote?
[indistinct chatter]
MIKADO: Masaomi...
♪ ♪
That took forever.
I mean, we were only going over
the plans for the school trip.
I never would have thought
the discussion
would get so heated.
‐ I didn't either.
By the way, Mikado,
is anything going on?
‐ Huh?
Why do you ask?
ANRI: It's just somehow
you don't seem the same.
‐ Uh, oh, sorry about that.
Was I spacing out a little?
‐ No, that's not what I meant.
I just wondered
if something happened
that made you happy.
‐ Huh?
I wanna tell her
about how I chatted
with Masaomi yesterday.
But...
I don't wanna make her worry.
Mm‐mm, nothing
that I can think of.
Come on.
Let's go home.
♪ ♪
AOBA: Hey, Mikado, Anri!
BOTH: Huh?
I can't believe your
committee meeting ran this late.
You guys are working hard.
[chuckles]
MIKADO: So, are you here
for club stuff?
‐ You got it.
I joined the Art Club.
Hey, you wouldn't happen
to have free time tomorrow,
would you, Mikado?
‐ Uh‐‐
‐ Well, yeah.
In case you forgot,
my tour of Ikebukuro
got sidetracked the other day
and we never finished.
So I thought if you're free,
we could try it again.
‐ Oh, yeah, forgot.
I'm not really sure
what Masaomi's warning meant.
So I guess...
Uh, I'm sorry,
but I've got some plans
I don't think I can get out of
this weekend.
‐ Aww.
Guess I'm out of luck.
Well, hey,
then what about you, Anri?
[both gasp]
‐ [quietly] I can't really say
I have any specific plans...
MIKADO: Wait.
What's going on here?
‐ But still,
I don't know Ikebukuro,
so I wouldn't be very much help.
‐ Oh, you don't have
to worry about that.
I'm gonna go ahead
and research stuff on my own.
ANRI: But I'm afraid I'd only
get in your way if I came.
AOBA: Aw,
that would never happen.
Just being with you
is enough for me.
MIKADO: "Being with you"?
Does he have a thing for her?
ANRI: Please don't tease me.
AOBA: No, I mean it.
So what time should we get to‐‐
‐ Wait a sec.
‐ Hmm?
‐ I was a little mixed up
on my schedule.
Tomorrow, right?
I'm actually free tomorrow.
‐ No way! Seriously?
MIKADO: What?
He's happy?
But only during the day,
all right?
The nights are, you know,
a little unsafe
with all those people
walking around.
‐ Sure thing.
Whatever you say.
[chuckles]
MIKADO: Hmm.
CELTY: Without even knowing it,
I had taken a step
from the ordinary
to the extraordinary.
There was a traffic light
I shouldn't have crossed,
and yet I still crossed it.
[Cóiste‐Bodhar neighs,
engine revs]
VARONA: Good evening,
my brave knight of Halloween.
Play time for children is over.
Is a shame.
[tires squeal]
[indistinct chatter]
CELTY: The ordinary life
I led until then
slipped away in an instant.
Now I realize my life is
immersed in the extraordinary.
Which makes me wonder...
WOMAN: She's driving away!
CELTY: When exactly
did it all begin?
WOMAN: She's getting away.
WOMAN: What?
WOMAN: Who was that?
[overlapping chatter]
[dramatic music]
MAN: What's going on?
WOMAN: It's the rider!
[all talking at once]
MAN: Where's the head?
♪ ♪
[horn honks]
SLOAN: Back so soon?
Are you changing?
VARONA: Affirmative.
SLOAN: It's a shame
I wasn't able to see that.
‐ I don't consider it
a shame at all.
I've killed the Black Rider.
I confirmed the headless corpse.
SLOAN: That's good to hear.
‐ Job was too easy,
and Black Rider
was beyond feeble.
Is too bad.
MIKADO: [sighs]
What am I doing?
Did I screw up?
[sighs]
TARO: Good evening.
Nobody's online, huh?
Did everyone go someplace?
I got on late,
but even Setton's
usually here by now.
[keyboard keys clacking]
SLOAN: By the way, while I was
waiting for you before,
a car with license plate 1‐3‐1‐3
passed by,
and now it's got me dying
of curiosity.
What makes 13
such an unlucky number?
VARONA: There are many theories.
Judas being the 13th man
to be seated at Last Supper
is one famous example,
but Christianity isn't
the only possible source.
Norse Mythology is another.
With only 12 gods,
there was harmony.
Loki, the 13th god, appeared
and disrupted that.
Ancient countries utilized
a duodecimal system.
The number 13
disrupts harmony of base 12.
A taboo number.
[computer chiming]
SAN: Good evening!
KYO: How are you, Master Taro?
‐ [gasps, exhales]
MIKADO: "Chatting
on a Saturday night
"does seem a little sad,
"and it's not really
my place to punish you,
"but if being punished
is what you really want,
"I'd be more than happy
to punish you
"within an inch of your life
with words.
"Now then,
it's time to find out
if you're an S or an M."
[chuckles softly]
TARO: Good evening.
You're the same as ever.
KYO: It's time to find out!
TARO: All right, we get it.
VARONA: As soon as they locate
the child we're to abduct,
they'll send word.
Until that time,
perhaps would be best
to take care of other job.
‐ Yeah, is good idea,
but are you sure you want to?
I know you're not thrilled
about job.
♪ ♪
To think he wants us
to torment some little girl.
I wonder if client's payback
is warranted?
No, it doesn't thrill me,
but I have no issue with it.
‐ Then if is no problem,
let's get over with.
♪ ♪
‐ I'm utterly bored.
This city is disappointment.
[computer chimes]
‐ Hmm.
TARO: Hey, good evening.
MIKADO: "Well, well,
looks like another
"wandering weekend traveler
has arrived.
"If you stay cooped up
inside your home,
you'll end up dead."
"I'm sorry."
TARO: What're you
apologizing for, Saika?
And who are you to talk, Kyo?
KYO: I'll have you know
that San and I
spent all day out on the streets
of Ikebukuru
living our lives
to the fullest.
First, we ate every variety
of gyozo they had
at Nanjatown's Gyoza Stadium,
and then the World Import Mart,
and we shopped at ALPA,
the specialty retailer.
After which we witnessed
a dashing gentleman
apprehend a thief
on 60 Story Street.
It was quite thrilling.
MIKADO: What?
‐ They actually witnessed
somebody catching a thief today?
SAN: The gyozo was really good!
TARO: A thief?
That must have been intense.
‐ "That reminds me,
has anybody here
"ever heard of something
called the Dollars?
"A sinister darkness
haunting the city.
"A flowerbed of evil
in full bloom.
Wonderful and dreadful
at the same time."
ANRI: "Dollars."
"I've heard a little."
"I don't really know much."
"You could say
they're like a color gang,
only they don't really have
a color."
KYO: "They're a deranged group
that blends in with the city."
TARO: "That's an exaggeration."
KYO: "How can you
be so sure about that?"
"The fact is that the Dollars
are obviously picking fights
with people
from another prefecture."
TARO: "What?"
SAN: "I heard that too.
"People from Saitama.
Some of them got taken out
by the Dollars."
TARO: "Is that true?"
KYO: "There were rumors
about it on pcry,
that social networking site."
TARO: "I'll do a search.
Sorry.
"I've got something else
I gotta take care of today,
so I need to head out."
[computer chimes]
♪ ♪
KYO: "In that case,
it's probably about time
for us to call it a day too."
SAN: "Good night!"
KYO: "Well, then,
have a great weekend everybody.
"Remember to be safe out there!
"You know,
now that I think about it,
"Setton, Kanra, and Bakyura
never showed up today,
did they?"
SAN: "Good‐bye."
‐ [exhales sharply]
♪ ♪
SAIKA: "Good night.
"I'm sorry
I didn't make it in time."
♪ ♪
CELTY: No matter how I try,
I don't get it.
Did this happen because of fate?
Or was it a trap
that someone intentionally set?
♪ ♪
[Cóiste‐Bodhar neighs]
Still, I wasn't the only one
who was thrust
into the extraordinary
without a clue as to why.
♪ ♪
‐ [breathing steadily]
SHINRA: It's gonna be okay.
She's sleeping soundly now.
[soft music]
[gunfire on video game]
Internal medicine
isn't really my thing,
but I could tell
she was showing some signs
of an inflamed pharynx.
‐ What is it?
Is she teething?
‐ I think we can rule that out.
She's a little too old for that.
That sort of thing
only affects infants
or occasionally toddlers,
but I guess since your brain
is basically like an infant's,
it wouldn't be too far‐fetched
for you to run
a teething fever your‐‐
[grunts, groans]
‐ Oh, yeah.
SHINRA: [groaning]
‐ [growls quietly]
MIKADO: I wonder
if this has anything to do
with Masaomi's warning.
[cell phone ringing]
Masaomi?
Hello?
Mikado speaking.
IZAYA: Hey there.
It's been a long time, Mikado.
Or should I call you
Taro Tanaka?
‐ Oh, Kanra,
you haven't called in a while.
IZAYA: I just read the chat log.
I heard something about
that Saitama incident myself.
MIKADO: Yeah,
I was just looking into that
to see what I could find out.
It must have been
some new members of the Dollars
going off on their own.
IZAYA: That's my guess too.
So what'll you do?
‐ I'd like to figure out
some way to stop this.
IZAYA: Why?
It's not like the Dollars
ever had a rule saying,
"Thou shalt not pick fights
in other prefectures,"
am I right?
And the whole point is
that you don't have any rules
in the first place.
‐ Yeah, but still‐‐
IZAYA: Or didn't you
learn your lesson
from that thing with
the Yellow Scarves a while back?
I heard that it created a rift
between you and that
former best friend of yours.
‐ No, that's not true at all.
Masaomi's still my friend,
even now.
IZAYA: [laughs]
[doorbell rings]
‐ [grunts]
Mm.
[soft jazz piano music]
♪ ♪
[footsteps shuffling]
[exhales]
[gasps]
["Never Say Never"
by Three Lights Down Kings]
[man singing in Japanese]
♪ ♪
SIMON: Next time,
we have story about Russians,
not about sushi.
My comrades very, very scary.
Scarier than
two‐week‐old fish heads.
Next episode,
"Moscow Does Not Believe
In Tears."
If you no get,
try looking it up.