["Headhunt" by Okamoto's]
[man singing in Japanese]
♪ ♪
KYOHEI: Who's Hollywood?
ERIKA:
And then they say
he strips every shred of flesh
off his victims
so there's nothing left
but the bone.
KURURI: What's that?
SHIZUO: Somewhere near here,
there's a sushi restaurant.
‐ This shadow cocoon thing‐‐
I can't seem to break out of it.
‐ I'm a monster, but so what?
Who gives a damn?
I don't care anymore!
[man singing in Japanese]
♪ ♪
RURI:
Why in the world did I end up
becoming
a bloodthirsty murderer?
♪ ♪
And why in the world
did I end up becoming a monster?
♪ ♪
It makes me nauseous.
I feel sick
every time I kill them.
No.
No. No.
This isn't right.
I can't let anyone love me.
I've got to become a monster‐‐
a monster no one understands.
And then they'll finally pay.
No. Not them.
Just the one.
I'm gonna kill him.
Him? Who?
Answer me.
Who? Where?
No! I don't want this!
Mom! Where are you?
Please save me. Save me.
SHIZUO: Bastards.
You're
a bunch of damn petty thieves!
‐ Shizuo.
MAN: In that moment,
the past reawakened
and flashed across the mind
of the serial killer Hollywood.
The monsters
she admired since childhood
doing as they pleased,
living their lives
without considering others.
Born into one of the wealthiest
families in the area,
she was forced to constantly
play the role of a blue blood.
‐ Huh?
MAN: That house is gone now.
Losing her family, fortune,
and all sense of honor,
in exchange,
she gained her freedom
for the first time.
RURI: In the end,
I got to meet a real monster.
Not a fake one like me,
but a genuine monster
with overwhelming power.
‐ This is fascinating.
She heals faster than anybody
outside of
Celty and your brother.
It's honestly
a little hard to believe.
Her life's not in danger.
She might even be walking soon.
‐ Thanks for doing this.
‐ Sure thing.
It's not like I can turn down
Shizuo's little brother.
Getting punched
all the way to Mars for refusing
isn't high on my bucket list.
YUHEI:
Sorry he's always troubling you.
‐ [laughs]
He looks out for Celty,
so I'm actually more grateful
than anything.
Hey, could I have some water?
I'm kind of thirsty.
YUHEI: Yeah, sure.
SHINRA: Thanks.
[Dokusonmaru meows]
SHINRA: Oh, she's awake.
Are you all right?
Probably just feels like
a dull ache, right?
I have to admit,
I'm a little geeked out.
Considering my line of work,
I never thought
I'd ever meet someone like you.
It's really an honor,
Ms. Hijiribe.
MAN: Ruri Hijiribe.
Born September the 27th.
Age unknown.
She's a popular idol
whose pale skin
and somewhat gloomy
yet attractive looks
give her an allure
that seems otherworldly.
She started as a makeup artist,
apprentice to Tenjin Zakuroya.
Her work on
"Vampire Ninja: Carmilla Saizou"
was critically acclaimed,
and she's rated
in the top 100 makeup artists
by the World Film Federation.
Later, she was scouted by
the Yodogiri Shining Corporation
and made her debut as a model.
She's been on a roll ever since.
‐ Hey, stop that, Dokusonmaru.
‐ Dokusonmaru?
‐ His full name
is Yuigadokusonmaru.
Cute, right?
‐ You ought to
give smiling a try
when you're holding a cat.
‐ Huh?
‐ It's kind of unnerving.
‐ I am smiling.
‐ [laughs]
If he ever met you, my dad
would want to dissect you.
[cell phone ringing]
Oh, I should take this.
‐ Yuhei Hanejima.
Is that you?
‐ Thank goodness.
You look better than I thought.
Water? You look thirsty.
[string music]
♪ ♪
‐ Sorry.
It's another urgent case.
What lousy timing.
How often do you get the chance
to meet Ruri Hijiribe?
‐ Thank you for coming out
in the middle of the night.
‐ My pleasure.
If you really want to thank me,
could you get me her autograph?
And one for Celty too, okay?
‐ I'll do my best.
‐ That's all I ask!
And I won't charge you
for this house call.
‐ Hold on. I can't‐‐
‐ Don't worry about it.
I'm planning
on gouging my next patient
for ruining this for me anyway.
Give my best to Shizuo, okay?
I'll show myself out.
[Dokusonmaru growls]
[door opens, shuts]
RURI:
What exactly am I doing here?
‐ You fell out of nowhere
right in front of my car.
I wasn't quite sure what to do,
so I brought you here
and called a doctor
to take a look at you.
‐ Why bring me here
and not a hospital?
‐ There are several reasons
I can think of.
Mainly,
I thought that a hospital
would be a problem for you.
‐ Huh?
YUHEI: May I ask you something?
‐ What is it?
‐ The serial killer they call
"Hollywood" in the news.
That's you, isn't it?
‐ Damn it.
What are you thinking,
bringing that injured
pain in the ass here?
SHINRA: That'll be 200,000 yen.
‐ [gasps]
You serious?
‐ I don't come cheap,
especially when your emergency
dragged me away from a chance
to spend time
with Ruri Hijiribe.
‐ Come on, two of you.
Fighting no good.
You must do
the "pain, pain, go away"
on Egor's injuries, doctor.
I beg you, please.
I'm 100% okay, all right?
SHINRA: Fine, I'll do my best.
Just get the money ready, okay?
By the way,
Egor is the patient's name,
right?
‐ Yeah, that's right.
We were in the same organization
back home in Russia.
But who the hell cares anymore?
‐ Oh! He picked up.
Izaya, it's Mairu.
‐ Yeah, what do you want?
Make it short.
I'm busy, okay?
MAIRU:
Does the name Celty Sturluson
ring any bells for you?
‐ Heh. Celty?
Yeah, I might know something.
Why do you ask?
MAIRU: What do you know
about this person?
IZAYA: Hmm.
I know
it has nothing to do with you.
‐ You do know something,
don't you?
I knew it!
Why won't you tell?
That's not fair!
[line clicks]
‐ What did he say?
‐ [growls]
Jeez!
I can't believe
he just did that!
He hung up on me!
So that's not gonna work.
Okay, let's see.
‐ I wish
I could turn my cell off
and ignore those two,
but I've got a business to run
here.
♪ ♪
‐ [grunting]
Shingen?
Oh. I'm sorry.
I mistook you for someone else.
‐ Hmm.
MAIRU: Hey there.
Feeling better?
‐ Are you all right, mister?
‐ I'm sure he'll be fine.
And plastic surgery
can do wonders these days.
Besides, you look kind of cool
bandaged up like that.
‐ Young ladies.
I haven't had the chance
to thank you for what you did.
I appreciate it.
‐ It's 200 large.
Come on, Egor.
Pay the doc.
‐ I'm afraid
I don't have any money.
It's unfortunate, but
I mishandled the job earlier.
The fact
that I didn't ask for an advance
is something I now regret.
‐ I'd like to put it up for you,
but we have to get stock
for tomorrow‐‐
‐ Stock day already?
Why not take day off instead?
We can make it holiday.
National Sushi Day‐‐
‐ Shut up, and get back to work.
‐ Hey, Mister.
‐ Huh?
‐ The money.
Want us to cover it for you?
‐ If that's what you suspected,
why didn't you turn me in
to the police?
‐ Did you want me
to turn you in?
If so,
you should've done it yourself.
‐ When you took me in,
didn't you think
I might attack you?
I'm gonna be blunt about this.
The way you're acting right now,
it's obvious that you're not
putting on some kind of act,
but to be honest, you're crazy.
‐ You really think so?
‐ I do.
Letting a murderer
come inside your home.
It's insane.
There was a very good chance
that doing this
would get you killed.
Did you ever stop
to consider that fact?
‐ So,
don't you think it's about time
you explained yourself, Dad?
‐ Uh, you see,
Egor's kind of what you'd call
a jack‐of‐all‐trades.
I hired him
to apprehend a certain woman.
‐ A woman?
‐ Right.
Do you know about
that serial killer, Hollywood?
Well, after investigating
that incident at Nebula,
I stumbled across a woman
whose ancestors had
an interesting
genetic abnormality.
Rather than let her be arrested
and given the death sentence,
I thought we could take her in,
dissect her,
pump her full of her drugs,
have a good time‐‐
you know, the usual thing.
What do you think?
‐ I'm not so sure, Dad.
How about you show
a little restraint for once?
SHINGEN: I'm surprised to hear
that from you of all people.
Whatever.
I hear she got clobbered
by someone on the street,
so how impressive could she be?
It didn't sound like
much of a specimen.
You may as well ignore this.
‐ Say, Dad.
This woman of yours.
Could it be...
is her name Ruri Hijiribe?
[instruments clang and clatter]
SHINGEN: How did you know?
I see, Shinra.
It's clear now
that you must've read my mind.
Spending so much time
with a Dullahan
must have awakened a special‐‐
‐ May I ask you something else?
‐ What now?
‐ If it's your intention
to kill me,
would it be to silence me?
‐ That might be one reason.
No. I can't kill him.
I can't kill anyone,
aside from them.
‐ Then you're better off
not going through with it.
This building is full
of surveillance cameras.
I'm sure
they recorded me carrying you.
There's no purpose
in silencing me
since there's evidence.
‐ What if the reason was because
I simply wanted to kill you?
‐ Then I'd be out of luck.
I'd prefer not to be killed,
though.
‐ You surprise me.
‐ Because if I did die here,
I'd be left
with several regrets.
‐ [chuckles]
‐ Something funny about that?
‐ No. I just thought
it was weird to hear someone
as robotic as you
talk about regrets.
‐ Maybe, but if there's
a girl right in front of me
on the verge of tears,
I have to say,
my life's biggest regret
would be dying
and not helping her.
‐ Are you trying to win me over?
Or just trying
to save your own neck?
‐ Who knows?
I'm not completely sure myself.
I've been told quite often
that I don't understand
people's feelings,
and they also say that they can
never tell what I'm thinking.
I have to agree with them.
Even so,
if you don't even attempt
to dry the tears
of a girl crying out for help,
you're the lowest kind of man.
‐ Hold on.
That's one of Carmilla Saizou's
lines, isn't it?
‐ Yes. He's one of the people
I truly respect.
‐ "Truly respect"?
But he's nothing
but a character you played.
‐ True enough, but whether
it's a serial killer,
a stupid thug,
or a cross‐dresser in love,
I have nothing
but the highest respect
for all the characters
I've played.
Perhaps because of an older
brother who's too emotional,
I lack some key things
that a human should have.
So
that's why
I decided to become an actor‐‐
so that, in some way,
I'd be able
to share the human emotions
of all the different characters
I play.
‐ [gasping]
Think positive.
He's way more human than I am.
He's a monster
who wants to become human.
[sighs]
I'm sorry.
I never actually thanked you
for saving me.
Thank you.
I mean it.
You saved my life.
‐ Please, forget it.
‐ Huh?
‐ The one responsible
for hurting you‐‐
was he a guy
dressed as a bartender,
by any chance?
‐ Why? Do you know him?
‐ Yeah.
But I'll tell you the details
some other time.
I should apologize too.
‐ Apologize?
‐ By the way,
I had to do something
that I hope you're okay with.
‐ What was that?
‐ Well, you see,
there was someone
who looked kind of sketchy
tailing you earlier.
So I took
some security measures,
just in case.
‐ It's all there.
Let me know
if you need me again.
‐ Cut us a deal next time.
‐ That'll depend on the case.
I'll see you later.
Jeez Louise.
What a day.
Classic example
of "when it rains, it pours."
Getting two cases
in just one night?
Guess I'll go back‐‐
MAN: Hey, isn't that the guy?
‐ To Yuhei's apartment and‐‐
MAN: Yeah, it's him, all right.
‐ Excuse me, sir!
You're the man
who was recently seen
leaving Yuhei Hanejima's
apartment, aren't you?
‐ Eyewitnesses
spotted him kissing
the actress Ruri Hijiribe
in front of his building.
Care to comment?
‐ Hey, hold on a second.
‐ What kind of house call was it
at this hour?
You aren't an OB‐GYN, are you?
‐ Fine, gentlemen.
I do have a statement
I'd like to make at this time.
And I'll be covering all that
and more
right after
the commercial break,
so stay tuned!
[men yelling]
I'm home.
[sighs]
I had a pretty rough day.
Where are you, Celty?
I'm totally exhausted.
‐ A fetish for neglect
is something
that I have a hard time
wrapping my head around.
‐ So, uh, Mr. Shiki,
why are you here?
Is there an emergency?
‐ Not today.
But take a look at this.
[men yelling]
‐ Who tipped you off
we'd be here?
MAN:
We got an anonymous phone call.
‐ Well?
How long have you been dating?
‐ We saw
a man in a white lab coat
leave this building‐‐
what was he doing here?
‐ You'll have to excuse us.
I'll explain at a later date.
‐ Hey! Hang on!
MAN: How'd you two meet?
MAN: Come on!
MAN:
Find that guy in the lab coat!
YUHEI:
I'll take you somewhere safe.
I'm going to have someone else
take over from there.
‐ And who would that be?
‐ A transporter
my brother talks about a lot.
I hear she can be trusted.
‐ This article mentions
an OB‐GYN
they tried to interview.
I'm guessing that was you.
‐ Yeah,
it certainly looks that way.
‐ Some of my younger associates
got roughed up
pretty bad near there.
So you see,
that makes me kind of curious.
Tell me‐‐
you didn't happen to examine
Ruri Hijiribe, did you, Doc?
‐ Sort of, yeah.
‐ So, then,
let's just cut to the chase.
What exactly is that girl?
SHINRA: I need a favor first.
I'd like to get out
of this black cocoon thing.
Would you mind
giving me a hand with that?
‐ What the heck
did you do that for, Erika?
‐ If we're talking moe,
it's something
that's in the eye
of the beholder,
you got that?
Your thinking's all wrong.
‐ No. You've got it wrong.
Talking about moe
in connection with panty shots
is an established technique.
Romantic ideals
informed by various fantasies‐‐
‐ Hey,
would you guys knock it off?
Quit spouting that crap
with all these people around.
Man, get your minds off
all that damn 2‐D stuff.
‐ Jeez.
‐ Fine.
I can take a hint.
‐ That reminds me‐‐
don't you think
the latest figurines
sculpted by Yoen Zetsmu
are gradually getting
racier and racier hip lines?
‐ No way.
Historically speaking,
the heart and soul of his work
has always been
showing off midriffs.
All slender and‐‐
‐ Shut up!
I don't want to hear anymore
about 2‐D!
‐ What? But figurines are 3‐D!
‐ Hey,
what're you talking about?
They're 2.5‐D!
‐ [groans]
Compared to you geeks,
Saburo's obsession
seems completely normal.
‐ Yuhei's off the market.
‐ You okay?
‐ I can't believe
he's taken now.
How did this happen?
It's not fair!
My sadness can't be measured.
It's even bigger than‐‐
♪ ♪
‐ You better now?
‐ Yeah!
That totally cheered me up.
I got to say,
girls' lips are the best.
They're so soft.
‐ They are?
‐ Hooray for soft lips!
‐ I... feel nauseous.
‐ Come on! Give me one more.
Give me one more!
MAN: That's hot.
We ought to thank you babes
for putting on the show.
‐ So, what happened, guys?
I thought you were supposed to
meet up with Mikado.
‐ Yeah, we are.
Want to come too, Dotachin?
‐ Cut it out.
Even if I did go‐‐
MAN: Now, don't be like that.
We're just asking here.
That's all.
You know about the Black Rider,
don't you?
Come on. You don't want to hog
all that reward money.
‐ How about
getting on board with us?
‐ Who would've thought
we'd see such old‐school thugs
in this day and age?
‐ You chicks are filthy rich,
aren't you?
‐ Say something already.
KYOHEI: Hey, boys.
‐ Huh? Who are you?
‐ Since you're into
picking on little girls,
guess you must be
the famous pedophile gang, huh?
‐ Shut up, or die.
[grunts]
‐ You bastard!
‐ [crying out]
MAN: Son of a...
you'll pay for this!
‐ We should bail
before he brings his buddies.
‐ You look familiar.
‐ I'm Kyohei.
You're Izaya's sisters, right?
‐ What? You know our brother?
‐ Thank you for helping us out.
‐ You guys let me know
where you're headed,
I can get my guy
to drive you there.
‐ Yeah, that would be great.
We were actually planning
on wandering around Ikebukuro
this afternoon.
Plus, we're waiting
for a friend to call us,
but we don't have any idea
when they'll call
or where they're going to want
to meet up.
‐ What's that about?
Hey, Saburo.
It's me.
‐ That 10 mil is mine!
‐ Forget about it!
We saw the Rider first!
The 10 million bounty is ours.
Get back here!
‐ [sighs]
Don't they have
anything better to do?
‐ Yah!
Get back here, damn you!
‐ Huh?
AOBA: I'm really sorry.
Asking you to do this
on our day off.
MIKADO: It's no big deal.
We didn't have plans anyway.
‐ Mm‐hmm.
‐ By the way,
I've been meaning to ask‐‐
are you and Anri going out?
Just asking.
‐ N‐no!
It's not anything like that!
We're, uh‐‐
we're friends.
Just friends.
‐ Yeah? Great!
So that means
you're available right now?
Would you like
to go out with me?
‐ [gasps]
‐ I mean, I was kidding.
‐ Huh?
‐ Well, sure. Of course I was.
I was worried
you might get upset with me,
you being a Dollar and all.
‐ Oh, really? I'm glad
I proved you wrong, then.
♪ ♪
‐ You were there that other day.
Weren't you?
‐ Th‐there?
Where's that?
‐ When we were getting thrashed
by Kadota's guys.
‐ Yeah, we saw you
at the deserted factory
with the Black Rider, right?
‐ Since we're not wearing
our yellow scarves,
we caught you
with your pants down, didn't we?
[Cóiste‐Bodhar neighs]
MAN: That morning, Ruri Hijiribe
was delivered safely to her home
by a transporter
on a black bike.
RURI: Uh, um, thank you
so much for doing this.
So, about your fee...
‐ This one's on the house.
‐ Huh?
‐ I actually enjoyed myself.
After all,
I almost never get the chance
to meet someone
with special powers like you
in this city.
‐ How'd you know?
‐ Somehow, I could sense it.
You could say you give off
the same "scent" as me.
‐ Hold on.
Are you trying to say
that you're‐‐
that all of those rumors
I've been hearing on TV
are true?
You aren't human?
‐ No.
‐ [gasps]
‐ [laughing]
MAN:
That was when it struck her‐‐
that this was a vast world.
Even phantoms and monsters
could enjoy life.
RURI: Even me.
Even Yuhei!
Even that Headless Rider!
Why?
All this time...
why didn't I realize?
["Never Say Never"
by Three Lights Down Kings]
[man singing in Japanese]
♪ ♪
CELTY: The recent incident
that rocked Ikebukuro
will be resolved at last.
IZAYA: But that turned out to be
nothing more
than a short‐lived day off,
and a certain man
predicts another uproar.
CELTY: Next time‐‐
IZAYA: "When in Rome,
Do As the Romans Do."