["Headhunt" by Okamoto's]
[man singing in Japanese]
♪ ♪
[Chikage and Kyohei yelling]
MIKADO: All this...
this is the last thing
I wanted us to become.
MAN: Ms. Akane!
SLOAN: I have our target.
Akane Awakusu.
Unharmed.
MASAOMI: Well, then,
I'm headed out
to meet my friends.
‐ B‐b‐bomb!
ANRI: I'm not a human.
But I'm not a monster either.
I'm just a parasite.
♪ ♪
[all grunting, yelling]
[Walker laughing]
[intense percussive music]
[distant booming]
♪ ♪
[Mikado gasps]
It's Shizuo.
‐ Yeah, that's right.
What do we got here?
Oh, I know you.
You're that kid.
A friend of Celty's, aren't you?
‐ Yeah.
Um, I'm Mikado.
‐ Oh, yeah. You're also a member
of the Dollars, that right?
‐ What?
Uh, yeah.
‐ Got you.
Since it wouldn't be cool
not to tell anybody,
I'm gonna go ahead and tell you.
Listen,
I'm quitting the Dollars.
Nice knowing you.
‐ What?
But why do you want to quit?
‐ You saw that text, right?
I don't want to breathe
the same air as cowards
who think it's all right
to kidnap women.
That's all I have to say.
[Mikado gasps]
SHIZUO: Consider that my notice.
I'm no longer
a member of the Dollars, got it?
‐ What?
I can't believe that Anri
is really a Flame Haze!
I never would've guessed it
in a thousand years!
‐ Huh. The girl with the sword
is a friend of Rio's I met.
‐ Huh?
‐ Wait a sec.
Why haven't you run away yet?
‐ I don't know.
I guess 'cause Rocchi's here.
What? Look at that.
It's crazy!
‐ Huh?
[both grunt]
‐ Not good idea
to get in my way.
This will piss me off.
‐ I appreciate a good catfight
as much as the next guy,
but it really would be a shame
to mess up each other's
beautiful faces and bodies,
don't you think?
[booming approaches]
What the?
Hey, it's you.
‐ Shizuo, what's going on?
‐ I heard some punks
may have taken a girl hostage.
So what went down?
‐ Well, turns out
Walker and the others
already rescued her.
‐ Good.
I'm happy to hear that.
Hey, uh,
you wouldn't happen to know
whose bike this is?
‐ It's mine.
‐ Hmm.
Oh, I see.
My bad.
I thought it belonged
to the scum who took the girl.
I was gonna hurl it at them,
but if it's not theirs,
that wouldn't be cool.
I do have one question, though:
who are you,
and what are you doing here?
Oh.
Lovers' quarrel?
‐ Heh, heh.
Very funny.
‐ Well, which one of you
scumbags took that girl hostage?
Where the hell are you?
[men mumbling]
‐ Huh?
‐ Oh, was it you?
‐ Maybe.
So whatcha gonna do about it?
Huh?
Die, sucker!
[yelling]
‐ Are you kidding me?
You piece of trash!
[Asanuma yelling]
[men oohing]
Hmm.
[all yelling]
You bastards are really starting
to annoying me.
All right.
Now, back to looking
for that fleabag.
Huh?
What do you wa‐‐
Normally, I'm not in the habit
of beating up women...
but you better be fricking ready
for me to crush
that expensive‐looking helmet
right between my fingers!
[rock music]
‐ Sloan, I'll be back
to the truck in 30 seconds.
Please have a weapon ready.
SLOAN: Roger that.
I have the back of the trailer
opened up for you.
VARONA:
He's not like the black bike
or that girl with the glasses.
And he doesn't have that oddness
about him like those others.
No doubt about it.
This man is human.
♪ ♪
‐ I've got you!
Huh?
Akane.
What is she doing here?
[gunfire]
Who the hell are these guys?
Why kidnap Akane?
And why are they attacking me
all of a sudden?
‐ Akane, what was his name?
‐ He said to call him Izaya.
SHIZUO: I see.
So that's how it is.
This time you've gone too far,
you fleabag!
♪ ♪
‐ Somehow he survived
my first attack.
He's much stronger
than I thought.
Sloan, could you stop the car
for a minute?
SLOAN: Right away.
VARONA: Why didn't you
cover her with sheet
or hide her behind something?
SLOAN: Hey, don't ask for moon.
We're smack in the middle
of this huge city,
fleeing from the yakuza.
And on top of it all, we‐‐
‐ Quiet.
Be silent.
SLOAN: Huh?
[glass shatters]
[dramatic music]
♪ ♪
Wait.
What the hell is that?
VARONA:
Get the car moving, Sloan!
Do it!
Now!
‐ Right!
You got it.
[tires screech]
‐ All right.
I guess that's it for you guys.
Looks like Shizuo delivered
the final blow himself.
Let's call it a day.
Go on!
Go!
‐ Okay,
but what about you, boss?
‐ Someone's got to take care
of this sweet young thing.
MAN: Uh, sir...
‐ [giggles]
‐ Now scram!
MAN: All right.
MEN: See you, boss.
‐ I don't care for the Dollars
much,
but I've taken a shine to you.
‐ Right back at you, man.
‐ You get into trouble
in Saitama,
you give me a holler.
‐ And you try
not to destroy Ikebukuro, yeah?
‐ We'll see.
That depends on the Dollars,
right?
[glass shattering]
‐ [gasps]
[gunfire]
‐ [grunts]
VARONA: Where should I aim?
This guy seems to be
impenetrable wall of muscle.
He cannot train eyeballs.
Maybe there.
Sorry.
I was hoping to take you
on in a fair battle.
[trigger clicking]
[Cóiste‐Bodhar neighs]
[gasps]
The black bike?
‐ Hold on to anything you can!
[tires screeching]
[Celty gasps]
[Cóiste‐Bodhar neighs]
‐ [gasps]
‐ [grunts]
♪ ♪
‐ Why, Shizuo?
‐ Huh?
‐ Why did you save me
when I'm‐‐
I'm trying to kill you?
Why?
‐ I didn't know
you were still trying.
‐ I am, because...
‐ All right.
Let's forget about that for now.
Are you okay?
‐ Mm‐hmm.
‐ That's what's important.
Because if you get yourself
hurt, Akane,
you won't be in any shape
to kill me, right?
‐ Oh.
Mm‐hmm.
CELTY: Huh?
What the heck is going on here?
Oh, well.
They're both smiling,
so... whatever.
WALKER: So what was this
epic battle about, anyway?
‐ I'll tell you all about it
while we grab something to eat.
‐ Great, but you know, I heard
Russia Sushi closed early today,
so they're not open for dinner.
‐ Really?
That sucks.
‐ Do you want to go
to the Taiwanese place instead?
‐ I guess so.
‐ Cool.
Anri, you coming with us
or what?
‐ Yeah, I guess‐‐
ah!
[Erika laughing evilly]
‐ Ooh, Anri, there are
so many mysteries about you
and things I just have to know.
I love it.
Like that Japanese sword.
Where'd you hide it, hmm?
Are you really a Flame Haze
or just a cosplay‐crazed beauty
in glasses?
Or could you be
a humanoid version
of the phantom sword
with huge boobs?
‐ Or maybe you're just a horny
fool who needs to stop.
‐ Oh.
‐ Well, I suppose you
don't have to tell us
if you don't want to.
Us girls, we all have
our secrets, now, don't we?
‐ Exactly.
And you know what, Anri?
Even if you were
an evil demon king
plotting world domination,
I'm sure that we could still
get along with you as usual.
KYOHEI: What's wrong?
‐ Oh.
I'm sorry.
I was with Mikado,
but now I don't see him
anywhere.
ALL: Huh?
NON: Aw, Rocchi.
How are your wounds feeling?
CHIKAGE:
I'm the picture of health, baby.
After you patched me up,
I feel completely healed.
‐ You're such a liar.
Honestly, Rocchi,
I hope you get yelled at again
tomorrow
by Kyoboo and the others.
‐ Will you forgive me
if I give you a kiss?
‐ Only if you promise me
you'll never fight again.
MIKADO: Wait!
Hold on!
‐ Huh?
[panting]
‐ Hey, kiddo, what's the matter?
What's with all the drama?
‐ It's my fault.
I take responsibility.
‐ Yeah?
For what?
‐ Hey, Rocchi, this is him.
This is the boy
who tried to save me
from those goons earlier.
‐ That right?
So you're taking responsibility
for not being able
to protect her?
Don't worry about that, kid.
In fact‐‐
‐ Hold on.
That's not‐‐
that's not what I mean.
Hear me out.
It was me.
I started it all.
‐ Huh?
‐ I'm the leader of the Dollars.
I created them.
And I heard what they did
to you and your men.
So please,
you can blame me for all of it.
And yes, I know I deserve
whatever you want to do to me.
But please, I beg you
not to destroy Ikebukuro
anymore!
Please!
‐ Okay, buddy.
Listen, a man should never
be so quick to grovel.
Especially not
in front of a woman.
‐ But I thought‐‐
‐ You know,
if I just go and beat up
some pathetic kid on the street
in front of my girl,
then I'd be the lame one, right?
[chuckles]
And why would I believe
that a plain‐Jane guy like you
is even the leader
of the Dollars
in the first place?
On the other hand,
I don't think you're lying.
‐ Oh.
Well, then.
CHIKAGE: But I can't just take
your word for it, right?
Whoever founded the Dollars,
here's what I know
about that bastard:
he's a freaking lowlife
who gets off
watching on a monitor
as his gang grows on its own
and starts fighting
amongst itself.
And I just can't imagine a guy
with an honest face like yours
doing something like that.
Then again, if you really are
the mystery guy
who created the Dollars,
why don't you let me give you
a few words of advice?
You should get out of it
while you can.
This thing is way too heavy
a load for a naive kid.
You should be living
the ordinary life.
Sure, it's not as exciting,
but take it
from a lowlife like me,
you'll be happier
in the long run.
No point in forcing yourself
to become something
that you're not.
MIKADO: When he said all that,
did he have any idea
what it would mean to me?
Could he know that his words
would negate my whole being?
It wasn't that I was afraid
of being left behind
by the Dollars as they changed.
I was afraid
of being left behind
by this city.
In his eyes
and in Shizuo's and Kyohei's,
my anguish was nothing
but childish nonsense.
How could the city
leave me behind?
The truth is,
I never caught up with it
in the first place.
[weeping quietly]
[dramatic piano music]
♪ ♪
SAIKA:
So nobody's online today?
It's lonely.
Sorry for saying that.
I'm weird.
I'm really sorry.
♪ ♪
‐ Huh. So whatever did happen
with all of that?
‐ Well, I'm not so sure myself.
Shinra gave me a call.
Said,
"You've been proven innocent.
Everything's okay."
‐ That's cool,
but why was the Awakusu group
going after you
in the first place?
‐ Well, I'm not at liberty
to talk about that.
‐ Huh?
‐ You see,
Shinra smoothed everything over
with the Awakusu group,
but that's only on the condition
that I never breathe a word.
‐ Wow.
Well, I don't want to get you
in any more trouble.
‐ I appreciate that.
SHIKI: You must be happy
that your daughter came back
safely, boss.
MIKIYA: Yeah.
‐ It was a strange situation.
I knew Shizuo Heiwajima
would never kill anyone.
From the information
I've received,
the person behind this scheme
intended to pin all of the blame
on the Asuki Group
by using a Russian hit man
named Sloan or something.
I'm not certain,
but it seems to me
the plan was
to give us the upper hand
when we met with them
for peace talks.
And then Shizuo's involvement
messed it all up.
‐ Well, if I had gotten caught,
they definitely would've had me
by the balls.
I had no choice but to frame him
for the murders.
‐ So it was you after all, huh?
‐ Watch it.
Don't say that out loud.
‐ I'm sorry.
You're right.
So these three guys
who were murdered,
they were spies?
‐ Uh‐huh.
One was a cop
and one was from
the Asuki Group,
and I guess
the third was some foreigner.
They never even saw
what hit 'em.
‐ Sounds like
a good housecleaning.
MIKIYA:
I don't need your approval.
‐ Course not, boss.
What about the loose ends?
‐ Akabayashi and Aozaki
are on their way.
♪ ♪
‐ Wait,
they doing it themselves?
‐ They said
they wanted to meet up
with their agent
in person first.
When I heard the details,
I have to admit
I was pretty surprised.
‐ Huh?
‐ But the way a parent
loves his child
is the same everywhere, right?
VARONA: I'd say
I'm 50% good mood and 50% bad.
SLOAN: Don't sweat it.
There is still time
to grab that Akane Awakusu,
and that other girl
in the glasses
should be easy prey.
VARONA: I suppose.
This city is great, isn't it?
Once we have this job
out of the way,
I can't wait to treat myself
by hunting down the black bike
and that bartender.
That'll be great.
[gulps]
And that is not the only thing
I want to do.
I insist we take vacation.
It's necessary.
‐ I guess I have no say on this.
Not even a veto.
AOZAKI: That's right.
‐ Huh?
AOZAKI: You have no veto power.
Please allow me
to introduce myself.
My name's Aozaki.
I'm sure
you know why I came here.
‐ You're Aozaki?
As in the street‐fighting
executive?
‐ You really know your Japanese.
I'm impressed.
‐ Here is what is unimpressive:
a big executive of organization
showing up all alone
to try and take on
people like us.
‐ Come on. Give me
a little more credit than that.
I'm not like that moron
over there.
[dramatic music]
‐ Pretty harsh, Mr. Aozaki.
There's only one reason
I came up here tonight:
'cause I heard
the perp who abducted Akane
was a gorgeous foreigner.
It's nice to meet you.
The name's Akabayashi.
And like that ugly
hatchet‐faced dude over there,
I'm one of the top dogs
of the Awakusu.
‐ And unlike
that moron over there,
I didn't come alone.
[gunshots]
‐ [yelling]
‐ Sloan!
AKABAYASHI: Uh‐uh‐uh.
This is a real treat for me.
I don't often get to dance
with such a pretty young thing.
Level with me.
You're thinking
that the Awakusu group
is half‐assed compared to you.
I mean, you've been
fighting mercenaries.
Yeah, we know about that.
[chuckles]
I admit you're very strong,
but keep in mind,
if you get too carried away,
things will only get
more painful.
Also, if you can get taken down
this easily,
going after Shizuo Heiwajima
is nothing but a pipe dream.
You can wind up dead,
and believe me,
if the daughter
of our new business partner
were to get killed on our watch,
we'd have a big problem.
Right?
♪ ♪
‐ Egor?
‐ [gasps]
‐ It's been a long time,
you two.
‐ This gent here
was the one who approached us.
Your old man and the president
of a weapons company
said that in return
for giving us a sweetheart deal,
all I have to do
is pretend I never saw you.
♪ ♪
‐ Screw your deal.
If you kill Sloan,
you must kill me.
To accept such pity as this,
my life would be worthless!
‐ [laughs]
You don't know
what you're talking about.
Good night.
‐ Varon‐‐
[grunts]
‐ [grunts]
I suppose we can do
whatever we want
to this poor bastard, right?
‐ Sorry we missed the fun,
Captain Akabayashi,
but you can leave the rest
to us.
‐ I was counting on that.
A cute one like this
killing herself‐‐
I don't think
I could sleep at night,
if you know what I mean.
‐ Nothing to worry about,
Akabayashi.
When you can't sleep, I'll tell
what best thing for you is.
You've got to eat some shark.
I'll get you the best there is
and shark fin soup too.
‐ Thanks.
I'll be sure
to stop by sometime.
‐ Okay.
Let's go.
MAN: [speaking foreign language]
‐ So, Mikado, what did you want
to talk to me about?
‐ Well, I've been thinking
long and hard about the Dollars
and how things currently are,
and it's just not right.
It's not what I had in mind
when I first started this group,
but the Dollars
don't have rules,
so the moment I make rules,
they won't be the Dollars.
In order to get what you want
in a world without any rules,
you need to have power.
That said,
if you still would like
to help me
get that kind of power,
and if you really think
I can still be of use
to the Blue Squares,
then I'll take
the deal you're offering.
‐ Hey, that's awesome!
‐ Come on over here
and I'll draw up a contract
real quick.
‐ A contract?
‐ If you and I
are gonna make a deal,
then it's only right
to put it in writing
and make it official.
‐ Huh?
[yells]
‐ Dude!
Aoba, you okay?
‐ Hey, what the hell
are you doing?
‐ Mikado...
tell me...
what's going on.
‐ I don't know why you did it,
but you dragged Anri into this.
You're getting what you deserve.
This is the very first order
I'm giving as your leader.
You will accept my anger.
‐ [exclaims]
I accept that
and this too.
This bloody piece of paper
is our contract.
And as of today, Mikado,
you're leader
of the Blue Squares.
We're your pawns
to use as you wish.
With us under your command,
you can lead the Dollars
down any path.
‐ Really?
[sighs]
That's great.
I'm so glad you're okay with it.
And I'm really sorry
about your hand.
Oh, I brought some bandages
and antiseptic with me.
Let me take care of that
for you.
Now, make sure you keep your
hand...
There's no going back now,
but surprisingly,
I don't feel any regrets.
I'm gonna do what I can
to return the Dollars
to what they should be.
If I can do that,
I can hold my head up high
when I face Anri and Masaomi.
♪ ♪
Sorry, Masaomi.
You warned me
to stay away from the Dollars,
but I couldn't do it.
I'm sorry.
♪ ♪
IZAYA: Yes, that's fine.
Right.
I understand.
I really believe the Asuki Group
is the best outfit
to run Ikebukuro,
that's all.
And I hope
for your continued support.
Looks like I resolved that issue
in just a day.
[cell phone vibrating]
JINNAI: Oh.
Hello.
Is this Mr. Izaya Orihara
I'm speaking with?
‐ Yes, this is Orihara.
JINNAI: I have to tell you,
I'm at the end of my rope here,
thanks to you getting
that monster mixed up
with the Awakusu Group.
It's really thrown me
off my game plan.
Seriously, if Akane Awakusu
hadn't gotten involved
with Shizuo Heiwajima,
things would've gone
much more smoothly by now.
‐ Hey, who the hell is this?
JINNAI: [laughs]
No need for you to know my name.
But as a token
of our new friendship,
let me offer an opinion...
or rather, a warning.
You're a bit too good‐looking,
Izaya.
‐ What?
JINNAI: It makes you stand out
in a crowd,
so in your case,
trying to blend in
really isn't an ideal way
for you to hide.
Besides,
you're looking kind of stressed.
I think a nap
would do you a world of good.
[thud]
[Izaya grunts]
MAN: Whoa.
WOMAN: Is he okay?
Just fell over.
JINNAI: Oh, and since you asked,
my name is Jinnai Yodogiri,
and I'm pleased
to make your acquaintance.
‐ Damn.
I underestimated them.
[freewheeling jazz music]
♪ ♪