["Headhunt" by Okamoto's]
[man singing in Japanese]
♪ ♪
‐ Not good.
Not good. Not good.
Not good. Not good!
MAN: Look at that!
It's a huge black object!
‐ What's its deal?
What the heck
am I even looking at here?
KYOHEI: Who's Hollywood?
WALKER:
It's that murderer's nickname.
‐ Let's go.
I want to see.
It's all happening
right around here.
So come on.
I can't take it anymore!
CELTY: It's gone!
I dropped it somewhere.
I must've dropped it!
♪ ♪
MIKADO: The city of Ikebukuro
never sleeps.
Strangely, two shadows appear
on the same day.
Whether by destiny or chance,
they meet in the city at night.
[tense electronic music]
♪ ♪
‐ You bastards!
You're a bunch of
damn petty thieves!
TOM: Hey, Shizuo.
I think that's about enough.
‐ Damn it to hell.
I got to carry all this cash
in my bare hands at this hour?
Those worthless punks.
‐ They didn't seem like
your typical thieves.
‐ I'm gonna go look
for an attaché case or something
to carry this in.
‐ Sure.
It's weird, though.
Who in this town
would pick a fight with Shizuo?
They must've been newbies.
KANRA: Hiya!
Kanra's in the house.
TARO: Hello.
BAKYURA: Yo!
SAIKA: Evening.
I look forward to chatting,
everyone.
KANRA: Right, then.
Has everyone gotten the hang
of this new chat room?
TARO: Yeah.
It's a lot easier now
to tell who's who.
BAKYURA: Damn right!
With these new icons,
it'll be more vivid
when I beat the shit
out of Kanra.
KANRA: Seriously?
Oh, no.
What're you gonna do?
BAKYURA: Troll ya, and ban ya,
on endless repeat.
TARO: Bakyura,
you're too cruel to him.
SAIKA: Let's all get along...
BAKYURA: Oh, Saika.
It's not like I hate Kanra
for real or anything.
IZAYA: You're the same old liar,
aren't you?
You know that, deep down,
you hate my guts.
MASAOMI: Shut up, Troll Ted.
SETTON: Evening.
TARO: Hey.
Good evening.
SETTON: I'm done.
It's hopeless.
TARO: What do you mean?
What happened?
SETTON: Well, I lost some money.
BAKYURA: What?
TARO: Aw, that's too bad.
KANRA: Yeah?
How much money was it?
SETTON: My entire month's pay.
SAIKA: Are you okay?
BAKYURA: What?
TARO: That's so awful.
You gonna be all right?
SETTON: Yeah.
I have a lot saved up,
so I can get by,
but it's still depressing.
KANRA: Cheer up, okay?
Oh, right.
I've got good news for you,
Setton.
SETTON: What?
KANRA: Ta‐da!
Check this out.
MAX: Hi!
‐ [laughs]
‐ Ladies and gentlemen!
Mommies and daddies!
I'm the President
of Jack‐o‐Lantern Japan,
Max Sandshelt!
Pleased to meet you.
Did you guys all see
that exciting news
that just happened earlier?
Right.
I'm talking about that story
where the Headless Rider
flew sky‐high.
Being all headless
was exciting enough,
but being able to fly
is even better!
I flippin' love it!
And then I got to thinkin'...
I'll hire the Headless Rider
and make her the next superstar!
That little pony's
gonna outdo Mr. Yuhei for sure.
So!
Here's the deal.
Someone out there's got to
find out who that biker is
and give me the lowdown.
Unless, of course,
you want to bring it in.
The reward is...
BAKYURA: 10 mil?
TARO: That's insane!
SETTON: There's no way
I'd ever be able to
catch the Black Rider.
It just wouldn't happen.
‐ Hi, I'm certain
you've all got to be
pretty confused
about what's going on here.
To explain this complex
and bizarre development,
let's first go back
to last night.
[stirring piano music]
[Cóiste‐Bodhar neighs]
♪ ♪
SHINRA: I'm home.
[sighs]
I had a pretty rough day.
Where are you, Celty?
I'm totally exhausted.
Huh?
What?
Hey! Hey! Hey, wait!
No! No, wait!
Heh,
I like to try new things too,
but I'm not used to this,
and I could go crazy
if my cup runneth over
with all this happiness.
‐ Mind staying with me here
for a bit?
‐ What's wrong?
You seem awfully depressed.
‐ [sighs]
Depressed isn't the word.
I can't get any lower.
Say something comforting.
‐ Whoa, what's with
all the negativity, my queen?
Hold on. So, on top of
dropping the million yen,
you also have
a bounty on your head
of ten times that amount?
CELTY: Yeah.
SHINRA:
Things'll work out, Celty.
Why don't you
just have some faith?
I'm sure that the money you lost
will find its way back to you.
They say
what goes around comes around.
♪ ♪
CELTY: Yeah.
I feel terrible.
I was planning
to buy you a present too,
but that went up in smoke.
Sorry.
Oh, it wasn't because
I wanted something in return.
It's just... well...
never mind.
Forget what I said.
‐ Celty!
You really are the best!
‐ Thanks, Shinra.
But I'm not in the mood now,
so don't get carried away.
‐ [laughing]
All right.
Then I'll just have to
look forward
to when you are in the mood.
[phone vibrating]
‐ A job came in.
I need to head out.
‐ You sure you're all right?
Maybe you should take it easy
for today.
‐ I'm fine.
Transporters have to
be dependable.
Don't worry.
I won't cause you any trouble.
‐ I'm fine
with any trouble you bring.
That's what family's for.
Bring it on.
‐ Thanks.
‐ That's a relief.
I'm glad she came around
and is finally
in better spirits.
Hold on.
Hey, Celty?
This shadow cocoon thing,
I can't seem to break out of it.
Hey, Celty.
Hello?
Are you there?
I can't get out.
[sighs]
And that's how
I got into this situation.
Honestly, I'd like to keep going
so that you know
what happens to Celty and me,
but to do that,
we'll need to rewind a little,
starting with Raira Academy's
opening ceremony two days ago.
There's an eccentric new student
this year...
‐ I'm Mairu Orihara.
That's "Mairu,"
as in "to dance and flow
down a field of origami."
Nice to meet you.
My favorite books to read
are encyclopedias,
manga, and porn.
And I swing both ways
when it comes to love and sex.
But I already have
a male bed partner in mind,
so just forget it.
As for girls,
I can go out
with as many as I want to,
so keep that in mind
when you ask me out.
SHINRA: And another new student
who happens to be
even more eccentric...
‐ I'm Kururi Orihara.
‐ Is there anything else
you'd like to share with us
at this time?
‐ Not really.
SHINRA: And a new student
who seems to have some baggage.
These two
are in the same class again.
[both chuckle nervously]
And they're
class representatives again too.
‐ Hey, Anri!
‐ Excuse me.
You're Mikado, right?
‐ Uh, yeah.
And your name is Kuronuma?
‐ That's right.
Aoba Kuronuma.
First year.
I was surprised when I heard you
introduce yourself.
I couldn't believe
it was really you.
‐ What?
Uh...
‐ Oh, I'm so sorry.
This is actually the first time
we've ever met.
‐ Oh, I see.
Um, then,
why were you surprised?
‐ You know.
It was because
you're a member of the Dollars.
SHINRA: He's not only
a member of the Dollars,
he's also one of the founders.
No way he can answer yes.
‐ What‐‐
what are you talking about?
[phones vibrating]
AOBA: Oh, I finally got it.
It's the Dollars' mailing list.
‐ [gasps]
‐ I'm Wakaba Mark.
‐ But how did you know
I had anything to do
with the Dollars?
‐ You remember
that first meeting
the Dollars had
in front of Hand's Plaza?
I was there!
You know what?
I kind of got the feeling
you were one of the leaders
of the Dollars
or something like that.
‐ You've got it all wrong.
There's no such thing
in the Dollars.
‐ Oh, I didn't know.
But still,
just getting this close
to a member of the group
is pretty exciting.
‐ Don't talk about it too much
at school, okay?
If you could keep it quiet,
that'd be great.
‐ Not a problem.
But could I get a favor from you
in exchange for keeping this
on the down low?
ANRI: An Ikebukuro tour?
‐ Yeah, one of the first‐years
asked me to show him around,
but I'm not that familiar
with the area.
‐ I'm not really either.
‐ I'm still at the point
where I'd get lost,
even with a guidebook.
‐ That's a serious handicap.
‐ So,
since you two seem like experts,
I was wondering if
you could tell me where to go.
‐ Let me think.
They've got to check out
Anime Café for sure.
‐ You can't say
they've seen it at all
if they missed out
on a visit to Swallowtail.
‐ And there's Namja Town too.
‐ And a real connoisseur
knows about Toshima Hall.
‐ As you can see,
it's probably gonna be tough
getting familiar with all these
places in a short time.
Hey, did you want us
to come along with you?
BOTH: Huh?
‐ Maybe it'd be better
to decide where to go
after we've met this kid.
I mean, we don't have any idea
what kind of stuff they're into.
‐ You guys don't mind?
‐ We don't mind at all.
I'm free,
as long as we go in the evening.
‐ All right, then.
To celebrate
this Ikebukuro tour,
let's sing
a traditional anime song medley!
‐ Pick a theme.
WALKER: Let's go with...
magical girl numbers
from the '90s tonight.
ERIKA: All right!
Book us for two hours.
WALKER: Easy, now.
ERIKA: Whoo‐hoo!
[Erika singing]
‐ Huh?
[gasping]
SHINRA: Every cell in her body
was screaming at her,
"That man is dangerous."
[door opens]
SHINGEN: You're the Sonoharas'
daughter, aren't you?
‐ What?
‐ I remember you.
You're Sonohara's daughter.
Am I wrong?
‐ I'm sorry, are you an old
acquaintance of my parents?
‐ Well,
I guess you could say I was.
Hmm, speaking of which,
how do I put this?
I also know about
a sword in your possession.
SAIKA: Oh.
He's my former owner.
I knew I recognized him.
Although he only let me slash
the soul of a bizarre monster
overseas,
and never humans.
SHINRA: The power within her‐‐
Saika‐‐
has uttered curses at her
for a long time.
And recently, it has grown able
to express its thoughts
more clearly.
‐ Excuse me.
Who are you?
Tell me,
what exactly do you know
about me?
‐ Hmm.
It's not an easy question
to answer, miss.
Perhaps I should say,
I know about you
to a certain degree.
Ah, whatever.
Forget it.
I know you're a powerful being,
but I don't think
you should take advantage
of weaker beings like me,
even if you're in trouble.
‐ I don't know
what you're implying.
‐ Here is my answer
to your other question.
‐ Aah!
‐ Forgive the intrusion,
my lovely young lady.
He and I were discussing
some important business.
‐ Excuse me.
I've got to go.
EGOR: The data you gave me
has all the details, correct?
You needn't
explain things further.
SHINGEN:
You'd best hear it, though,
or you'll regret it.
I can't have you dismissing it,
thinking it's a joke.
NAMIE:
Seiji's in his second year.
I wish
I could've congratulated him
at the ceremony.
‐ Congratulate?
It's not an entrance ceremony.
Guardians don't show up
to these things.
‐ Well, I wanted to be there.
Come to think of it,
I hear that your little sisters
have started to attend
Raira Academy themselves.
IZAYA: You have sharp ears.
NAMIE: Of course I do.
Your loyal servant always tries
to learn about her king.
‐ I don't like them.
Either one of 'em.
‐ Can't believe
you detest someone
other than Shizuo Heiwajima.
‐ Don't make fun.
You know how they have
skill sets in games, right?
Like how those good at magic
are bad at combat,
or how good fighters
are light on brainpower.
That's how my sisters are.
They're trying to compensate
for their own flaws
by forming
a well‐balanced party.
‐ [groans] I don't see
where you're going with this.
‐ It's simple, actually.
Those two deliberately
created personality traits
that were distinctly different.
Even though they're twins,
they each want to have
their own unique identity.
And by doing everything
together,
they think
they're incredibly competent,
deluding themselves
into thinking
they're capable of anything.
‐ Oh?
IZAYA: They chose their style
in grade school
by drawing straws.
Kururi wears gym clothes
despite being terse and gloomy.
On the other hand,
Mairu, the younger one,
looks like a bookworm
but acts like
a cheerful chatterbox.
‐ Is there some significance
behind
that contradictory behavior?
‐ Nope.
But for those two,
having looks
that do match what's inside
probably doesn't
hold any significance either.
Because in the end,
they're one person.
They're thinking as long as
all the parts are there,
then there's no problem.
Anyway, those two stand out,
no matter what crowd they're in.
‐ Hmm.
I see.
I guess it's no wonder
the aspiring master mind
doesn't want to spend much time
with him.
But are they
going to be all right?
If they stand out so much,
won't they wind up being
the targets of bullying?
‐ Hadn't thought about that.
It's unfortunate
when people get bullied,
although inevitable.
‐ Huh?
‐ [laughs]
I pity them.
‐ Hmm.
‐ [chuckles]
[all gasp]
I'm gonna give you
three seconds.
Who's the boss?
Point her out to me.
Three.
Two.
One.
Zero.
Whoopsie.
Thanks a lot.
Hey!
Not so fast.
You can't run away!
‐ Aah!
‐ Why don't we go to
the girls' room and have a chat?
You know what? Come on.
Pay attention, would you?
I don't even know
what your name is,
but for some reason,
I really, really want
to be your friend now.
[giggling]
SHINRA: After this incident,
the news traveled quickly
through the school,
and the girls set their sights
on another target‐‐
the other twin sister.
TEACHER: Let me ask you again.
You didn't do this yourself,
right?
‐ No, sir.
‐ Does anyone here know
who wrote
all over Orihara's desk?
Hmm.
‐ Tsukiyama did it, along with
some girls from another class.
TEACHER: Tsukiyama, I'll see you
in the faculty room.
And bring those girls
from the other class, got it?
TSUKIYAMA: Hey, you.
‐ Hmm?
Hmm.
Hmm?
What?
‐ Don't play dumb with me.
What exactly were you trying
to pull back there?
‐ Gee, are you ladies
asking me out?
I don't know what to say.
'Cause
I got to be honest with you,
I don't think I can handle
dating all of you
at the same time.
‐ What? Look, that stunt
in the classroom wasn't cool.
You think you're some kind of
lame‐ass hero
squealing on people?
‐ No, if I was a hero,
then I would've stopped you
when you were vandalizing
your desk, wouldn't I?
I mean,
what kind of logic is that?
‐ Then why didn't
you keep your mouth shut?
‐ Well, that's obvious.
You never asked me
to keep quiet.
And if you get right down to it,
if I have to choose
you or Orihara,
then picking
a quiet, big‐boobed,
mysterious girl in gym clothes
over a girl who vandalizes desks
is kind of a no‐brainer
in my book.
‐ Don't give me that crap!
‐ Hey, your bag.
[all scream]
[solemn piano music]
TEACHER: Unfortunately,
we couldn't pinpoint
the cause of the fire.
‐ I see.
‐ Sorry, Kuronuma.
You mind
if I take a look in your bag?
‐ Sure.
♪ ♪
TEACHER: Thanks.
Well, to be honest with you,
we found some paint thinner
in those girls' bags.
I wanted to rule you out,
just in case.
AOBA: Paint thinner?
‐ I know, right?
First few days of school,
and they're already in trouble.
Well, we knew
they were a bunch of bullies.
What a pain.
‐ Yeah.
♪ ♪
MAIRU: Yoo‐hoo!
Hey, there!
We haven't had
the chance to meet yet,
so I wanted to say hi.
My name's Mairu Orihara,
Kururi's younger twin sister.
Nice to meet you.
‐ Oh, um...
it's nice to meet you too.
‐ Thanks a lot.
‐ Huh?
Oh, that's okay.
There's really no reason
for you to thank me.
After all, I didn't stop them
from vandalizing your desk
in the first place.
‐ I know that.
‐ Huh?
‐ Well, you see, the truth is
that Kururi was
secretly watching them
vandalize her desk
from the hallway.
‐ Well,
if that was the case, then...
‐ She wasn't thanking you
for that.
You made her happy when you said
that she was cuter
than that Tsukiyama girl.
She's kind of lame
the way she's not very athletic
but goes around
wearing gym clothes, right?
Boys don't usually compliment
her like you did,
and that's why she's so happy.
‐ Be quiet.
Thank you.
‐ All right!
I got an indirect kiss
from Kururi!
[giggles]
I'm sorry.
I'm sure getting kissed by girls
who aren't even your girlfriend
is kind of a shock.
But even though my sister
may seem like the quiet type,
the truth of the matter is
that she's way more aggressive
than I am.
‐ That's not true.
‐ Oh, but even if you do
fall in love with her later,
you can't hog her
all for yourself, okay?
Because Kururi belongs to me,
got it?
Oh, and I should mention,
I've already got my heart set
on Yuhei.
Actually, since my sister's
also a huge Yuhei fan,
it's possible that kiss is as
far as you'll ever get with her.
[laughs]
See you.
‐ Hey, wait a minute.
BOTH: Hmm?
‐ I don't want to be rude,
but you didn't happen
to sneak something
into those girls' bags, did you?
Like...various things?
‐ Don't tell.
[both giggle]
SHINRA: It was after all this
that Celty's hardships
really began.
‐ You bastards.
You're a bunch of
damn petty thieves!
Wah!
SHINRA: Meanwhile,
after seeing it on TV,
the twins were desperate to meet
the Headless Rider in person.
[exotic music]
MAIRU: I wonder where
that glider could have gone.
I was so sure
that it was headed this way.
Man, I want to see it!
I want to see it!
Is something wrong, Kururi?
So what's inside the envelope?
[man groaning]
KURURI: What's that?
‐ Think you'd better stand back,
sis.
‐ [grunts]
‐ What's the deal with this guy?
Should we call an ambulance?
SHIZUO: No.
A hospital is no good.
Young lady,
do you know if there's a...
[retches]
‐ Are you all right?
SHIZUO: I'm sorry.
Before I die,
there's just one thing
I'd like to do.
‐ What is it?
We don't really get this a lot,
so we'll take requests.
SHIZUO: Somewhere near here,
there's a sushi restaurant
run by a Russian.
Do you know it?
‐ And here we are.
Though there's still more
of this story to tell.
[dead bolt snaps]
Is that you, Celty?
Thank goodness you're back.
Still,
the thought of a neglect fetish
did get me excited,
but when I realized it wasn't,
I still...
Huh?
‐ A fetish for neglect
is something
that I have a hard time
wrapping my head around.
[man singing in Japanese]
♪ ♪
MAN:
Let me tell you about a girl‐‐
the story
of a girl no one knows,
who's creepy, who's sad,
and gruesome.
Yes, the constantly changing
fate of this girl is tragic.
Next time‐‐
"Adding Insult to Injury."