["Headhunt" by Okamoto's]
[man singing in Japanese]
♪ ♪
‐ She's just trying
to beat you up.
Here's a tip, you gotta
hit 'em where it counts.
‐ We got a class about to start,
so cut the crap.
‐ Izaya was nice enough
to tell me
you're not your family's
business, Akane.
‐ I don't get the feeling
Izaya would be
an easy guy to impersonate.
‐ I'll leave him alone for now.
I better watch him though.
Give a punk like that an inch
and who knows what he'll do.
[man singing in Japanese]
♪ ♪
‐ Are we comfy,
Mr. Info‐Broker?
Speak up.
Or would you prefer I call
you Izaya Orihara instead?
So Info‐Broker,
do you have any idea
how you got in this mess
in the first place?
Here's a hint.
Have you ever heard
the name Mimizu?
[laughs]
Would you look at that?
I wonder if he's got
any other buttons I can push.
Those scary Awakusu boys
hired you to snoop on us,
didn't they?
Hello?
You listening?
HARUYA:
I know you're a busy guy,
but if you've go the time
I've got a job for you.
There's an outfit
calling itself Amphisbaena,
running a gambling ring
in town.
Problem is we can't pin down
where they're operating from.
The location's
always different
so players get an email
telling them where to go.
We rolled up
on a couple of them
that were using
a singles mixer for cover.
Legit places don't usually rent
their space out for gambling,
but they got it set up
to look like
some casual tournament,
using chips for collateral.
People are playing away,
but nobody's
cashing anything in.
All anyone's got on the table
are chips.
The chips they're using though,
they're IC chips.
‐ Neat idea except for
the risk involved.
If someone loses, they could
always blame the chips.
HARUYA: True, but Amphisbaena
doesn't seem to care much
about the risk.
If this was just about
them fleecing people
on our turf, we'd handle it
the way we always do.
But we don't know who's
behind these guys.
If it's an outfit like ours,
we want to know so there's
no misunderstandings.
[sirens blare]
[Cóiste‐Bodhar neighs]
You know one of our guys,
Akabayashi?
‐ Sure, he's your fixer
for Janjakajan, right?
HARUYA: Yeah, well,
the other day
he came down hard
on some punks.
He caught 'em dealing
this homemade shit
for some new outfit in town.
We've been trying
to find the supplier,
but it's nothing
but dead ends.
IZAYA: You think it might be
Amphisbaena?
HARUYA: Uh‐uh.
Those punks confirmed as much
after we put 'em
through the grinder.
They've been told to be on the
lookout for Amphisbaena, too.
‐ So is part of this job
you're offering to find out
who's supplying these dealers?
‐ Nah, you don't got
to worry about that.
We're using other channels
to look into 'em,
so we're good.
Although,
if a supplier finds out
we're looking
into Amphisbaena,
we'd have their attention,
and we don't like attention.
‐ You mentioned other channels.
What does that mean?
‐ Curiosity killed the cat,
Info‐Broker.
‐ Oh, sorry for being nosy.
It won't happen again.
‐ Hey, by the way,
you wouldn't happen to know
anyone named Nakura,
would you?
‐ Don't know, maybe.
Depends on if it's their
first or last name.
Come to think about it,
I might have gone to school
with someone called Nakura.
‐ Nah, I doubt it's
the same guy as this one.
He's been playing head games
with the boss's kid.
‐ His daughter's in grade school
for crying out loud.
What a shame.
No matter how safe
Ikebukuro is,
you have to watch out
for the bad guys.
Or even bad girls, I guess.
If Nakura is a girl.
‐ We'll drop you here,
if you don't mind.
‐ You usually let me off
where you pick me up.
Why'd you drive me here?
‐ Goddamn, you're suspicious.
There's nothing behind it.
You're getting out here,
'cause this is on my way.
The boss told me to pick up
his daughter, see?
‐ What a beautiful child!
You're Akane, right?
‐ Um, yes.
I'm Akane Awakusu.
Nice to meet you.
‐ Don't let me down
on that job.
I'm counting on you.
‐ Sure, I promise I won't
disappoint.
Ooh, that Mr. Shiki
is a sharp one.
Good thing I didn't deal
with Akane personally.
Mr. Kumoi is
really pissed off.
Instead of getting rid
of Akabayashi
like we were told to do,
we went and picked a fight
with a different gang
and even made the news.
After screwing up like that,
Mr. Kumoi's not gonna let us
get off easy.
Not by a long shot.
And I don't blame him,
'cause we've disgraced
Heaven's Slave.
[all gasp]
To make sure I knew
how bad we screwed up,
he used a dart on me.
He made me scream out
each note
as he carved them
into my arm.
When he started this,
the idea was to use the Dollars
as cover for us.
There's safety in numbers,
and if that meant being
number two, that was cool.
There's no shame in it.
But he says we still
don't have what it takes
to be number two.
He knows what
will get us there, though.
We're gonna take over
Amphisbaena
and their outfit,
'cause that's what
Mr. Kumoi wants.
It's now or never.
There's no turning back
for us.
MIMIZU: So Info‐Broker,
I bet you've done
your research on us.
Unfortunately for you,
the boss doesn't like people
sniffing around our business.
Personally, I'd love to share
some of our little secrets
with you,
but orders are orders,
I'm afraid.
You wouldn't happen to be
working for Heaven's Slave,
now would you?
I'll take that as a no.
How does that saying go,
silence is golden?
It's a good thing
you're not much of a talker,
since I let it slip that
I have a superior.
Here's what I found out
about you.
You have two cute
little sisters,
Kururi and Mairu, right?
You must be dying to see them
right about now,
so I sent someone
to go pick them up.
And I can't wait to meet them.
MAIRU: Izaya!
Time to die!
‐ It's nice to see how you
really feel about me, sis.
The older you've gotten,
the nastier you've become.
Oh, how modern society
has corrupted you.
‐ Ha, that's funny coming
from the king of corruption.
Next time you won't dodge
my attack.
‐ Izaya, you better?
‐ What do you think?
As long as I can avoid Mairu
breaking my neck, then yes.
Hmm?
‐ [grunts]
‐ [chuckles]
Oh, it's you.
For a second there,
I thought you were Shizu‐chan.
‐ Hiya, coach!
What the heck
are you doing here?
‐ Stay back, ladies,
'cause I'm gonna beat
the living shit
out of your brother.
‐ Sounds like fun.
Wanna watch?
‐ Mm‐hmm.
‐ It's times like this
I find it hard to believe
we're related.
Master Eijiro.
What's a professional
martial artist doing
attacking a civilian
on the street?
‐ Is that what you're
calling yourself these days?
Anyone who packs a knife
that can dodge my kicks
ain't no civilian, shitheel.
You think you can
waltz by my dojo
acting like nothing happened
between you and my sister?
You ruined her life,
you goddamn son of a bitch!
IZAYA: You want to do this
here in public?
How did I ruin Mikage's life?
I never touched her.
‐ It don't matter
if you touched her,
you slept with her,
or whatever, you piece of shit.
Mikage was a good kid,
got good grades,
was gonna make something
of herself.
Then you come around
with all your smooth talk,
and she dropped out of school!
[groans]
Damn, Mikage.
What the hell's that for?
You don't still got a thing
for this douche bag, do you?
‐ It's the only way
to shut you up
before everyone in town
starts thinking I sleep around.
Besides, picking fights
in the street?
You want to give our dojo
a bad rep or what?
‐ You snuck up on me
and kicked my ass.
How's that supposed
to help our rep?
‐ Oh, stop it, you big baby.
KURURI: Hey, where'd he go?
MAIRU: Who knows.
‐ A pro fighter's gotta be ready
for sneak attacks
at all times.
ELJIRO: Bite me!
‐ So this Mikage Sharaku.
Is she your girlfriend
or just a booty call?
Are you thirsty?
Can I offer you a drink
of water?
[laughter]
Oops, I spilled.
Could you get me some more
bottles of water?
‐ Sure, what kind?
‐ Two liters.
Three dozen of them.
And now it's time
for a quiz.
Question, what could I do
with that much water?
Meh, time's up.
The answer is pour every single
bottle over your head
nonstop until you suffocate.
Since you didn't answer,
here's what I'll do.
I'll force your little sisters
to drink it instead.
Ten liters each sounds fun.
You survive by profiting
off the dirty little secrets
of others.
But how will you survive this?
Oh, I'm sure you
gave it some thought,
but I doubt
you prepared for it.
Even if you had,
it wouldn't make
any difference, sweetie.
IZAYA: Hi, transporter.
I hope Shinra's doing better.
Nebula's lab
is state of the art.
Why, I bet he'll recover
faster there than at a hospital.
‐ How can you take this
so lightly?
You do know he was
almost killed, right?
‐ Yeah, well,
when I got stabbed,
he said, "See ya,"
and hung up on me.
Maybe I'm trying to outdo
his insensitivity.
‐ You said you had info
on the man who did it.
‐ I do, but let's talk
about the job first.
‐ I swear, if you're
lying to me about this,
I'll hand you right over
to Shizuo.
‐ I know, I know, but even
though I might be a liar,
I never lie when it comes
to business.
‐ Then why'd you bring company?
‐ Them?
Oh, you don't have to worry.
They're sort of like
foot soldiers/bodyguards for me.
CELTY: Dragon Zombies?
‐ I know, right?
There's a whole lot
of people who there
who resent me,
don't you know?
So I'm paying these fine folks
top dollar for their services.
‐ Back to business,
what do you want me to deliver?
‐ This will take you
a couple days, first of all.
‐ What are you talking about?
I have to stay here
and take care of Shinra.
I can't be gone
a couple days.
‐ It'll be fine.
You won't be working
the whole time.
Just moving around
a little every day.
‐ What does that mean?
‐ Raring to go, huh?
I want you to transport
some information.
[Cóiste‐Bodhar neighs]
‐ He was meeting
with the Black Rider.
‐ No doubt about it anymore.
He's got ties with it.
MAN: Yeah, so what does
Mr. Kumoi say?
‐ He found out Orihara's
been digging for info
on Amphisbaena
for the past few days.
MAN: So keep an eye on him?
‐ We can't let the Awakusu
take down Amphisbaena.
As soon as you get a chance,
grab that laptop.
When Akabayashi
nabbed our guys the other day,
I found out
we had a client
who plays big
at Amphisbaena's casino.
We used him to get some guys
on the guest list,
but after a couple times
we stopped getting invited back,
which means they
found out about us.
See this chip?
It can record your wins
and losses electronically.
That's not all, though.
There's a transmitter
and a bug inside.
It's a clever system
for tracking all their members,
and Mr. Kumoi
wants that system.
He wants to mass produce
the chips
and use them to expand
our business.
If we can team up
with Amphisbaena,
it'll be a win‐win
for both of our outfits
and no one will get hurt.
‐ So that's why we're
following the info‐broker.
‐ Uh‐huh, but if he's snooping
around for the Awakusu,
we want to get to him before
he has a chance to report in.
As soon as we get our hands
on that laptop,
we're gonna make‐‐
[phone chimes]
It's Mr. Kumoi.
He wants to see me again.
‐ Why?
‐ Guess he wants me
to scream some more.
MIMIZU: Want to know what else
I know about you?
You and the Black Bike
are besties.
I also found out
you had that urban legend
checking up on us
for the past few days.
Oh, and on Heaven's Slave,
too.
To be honest,
I don't know much about them,
but if they're going
to be a pain in our ass,
their days are numbered.
If you know anything
about them,
you should probably
tell me.
Do you want to live or not?
That wasn't water.
That was kerosene.
Oh, when I light you up,
you might want
to hold your breath
or you'll choke on the smoke.
I'm not sure how long
you'll take to burn out though.
[pounding on door]
Looks like
your sisters are here.
We'll do this later.
Let them in.
[all shouting]
HIROTO: At last we get to meet
Amphisbaena.
How's it going?
Don't worry,
we're not your enemies.
Or allies, yet.
‐ You are?
‐ Oops, sorry.
You can call me Shijima.
And we run the distribution
of Heaven's Slave in the city.
‐ Oh, right.
I've heard of you.
SHIJIMA: Hey, isn't that guy
under the bag
the info‐broker the Awakusu
hired to spy on you?
‐ Why, are you his friend?
‐ Not even.
But in a way,
he did help me figure out
where your hideout is.
[both grunt]
[both sigh, gasp]
[Cóiste‐Bodhar growls]
[whinnies]
MAN: Drive! Drive!
Ahh!
[Cóiste‐Bodhar neighs]
‐ [grunting]
[both groaning]
[both scream]
[beeping]
SHIJIMA: See this?
It's a program that uses
GPS to show the location
of your bugged chips.
‐ Where did you get that?
‐ Well, seeing as how
the laptop's his,
you should ask him.
Look, we didn't come here
'cause we want to fight you.
We'd much rather
do business with you.
That said,
we think it's better
if this info doesn't get
into the Awakusu's hands.
That's all.
[phone rings]
‐ Yes, hello?
[beeping]
Who is this?
Answer me!
MIMIZU: Hello?
‐ What?
‐ [echoing] Right, listen.
If you're‐‐
[gasps]
MAN: [distorted] Hi.
BOTH: Who is this?
MAN: Who?
I thought by now
you'd both know me well.
I'm Izaya Orihara.
You've heard of me, right?
So kidnapping?
That's low, but it brought us
all together.
‐ It can't be.
‐ What the hell?
MAN: I for one
am loving this,
hearing you lose your cool
and on the phone.
[laughs]
I know, let's have a pop quiz.
‐ What?
‐ What the hell is this shit?
MAN: Question one,
What do Tokage of Amphisbaena
and Mr. Kumoi of Heaven's Slave
have in common?
‐ [gasps]
MAN: Bzzz, too slow.
The answer is they both have
a mole under each eye.
‐ How do you know Tokage's
the boss?
Tell me!
How do you know
what the boss looks like?
MAN: It's about the gentleman
with the bag over his head.
Do you know if he has
moles under his eyes?
Yes or no.
Come on, tick‐tock.
‐ Huh?
MAN: Ehhh, sorry.
Question three.
Who do you think is the one
wearing that bag?
Could it be Tokage?
Or could it be Mr. Kumoi?
‐ No!
You're not the boss!
You can't be!
No!
‐ Mr. Kumoi?
Screw this.
I'm cutting him loose.
[gasps]
‐ Here, let me give you
a hand with that.
[suspenseful music]
♪ ♪
Ta‐da!
It's nice to meet you.
Are you surprised?
‐ Orihara?
‐ It is you.
‐ You know,
you might want to work
on your torturing technique.
I already knew
you were the squeamish type,
but still,
you could have at least
ripped my fingernails out
or something.
‐ But then who's on the phone?
MAN: [laughs]
[thud]
What the hell, Izaya?
All spoiling the surprise
and shit.
You bastard.
‐ What is this?
Why'd you‐‐why'd you let us
catch you?
What are you doing here?
‐ Good question.
I guess I'm here for
the same reason Shijima is,
more or less.
I came to try to talk you out
of this silly casino thing
you've got going on.
In all honesty,
I don't think you know the risk
you're taking going up against
the likes of the Awakusu.
See?
I'm not here to fight you.
I like you.
I'm here to people watch.
The sack was great.
You know I could
see through it.
I loved watched you get off
as quote‐unquote tortured me.
So cocky.
So cute.
[Mikage grunts]
‐ You gonna fight
or you gonna stand around?
Come on!
[all shouting]
‐ [gasps]
No, no.
Please!
[groaning]
MIMIZU: Don't just stand there!
Do something!
‐ I bet you want to know
how I got in here so easily.
Ha, I bet you want to know how
I untied myself so easily, too.
‐ All right, tell me.
‐ I'd be happy to tell you.
Although, I don't think
you're gonna understand
how I did it.
‐ Damn you.
What did you do to everyone?
‐ Like I said,
you're not going to understand.
Aww.
‐ [yells]
[grunting]
Ahh!
‐ Uh‐uh.
You didn't answer
any of the questions right.
Too bad for you.
You got a penalty round
coming your way.
Thanks for playing, gorgeous.
Better luck next time!
[Mimizu screams]
‐ Well, now that that's done,
is there anything else
I can do for you?
‐ Maybe there is.
That Mimizu girl's a tougher
nut to crack than I thought.
Izumii's not having much luck
with his hammer either.
Do you think you can
give it a shot?
‐ Sure.
But if I do what you want,
will you take me to see
Takashi like you promised?
‐ Maybe,
if you keep helping me.
In the end, it's up to you
whether it happens‐‐
‐ Oh, darn it.
If I was as strong as Anri,
I could have made you tell me
where Takashi is.
‐ Don't get down on yourself.
And you shouldn't
compare yourself
to Anri Sonohara either.
You're stronger than she is.
Remember, you did break free
from Saika twice.
Haruna Niekawa.
[gentle music]
So anyway,
Amphisbaena seems to have
shut down their casinos
and disbanded
their membership.
By the time I started
poking around,
their boss Tokage
was long gone,
vanished without a trace.
‐ He's not the only one
who disappeared.
About two days ago,
that gang of dealers
I told you about split town.
You wouldn't happen to know
anything about that, would you?
‐ Nope.
Who knows,
maybe they were finished off
by whatever was left
of Amphisbaena.
‐ You're a smart guy.
You think you've got
the world by the balls,
don't you, info‐broker?
‐ Not at all.
Besides,
how boring would that be,
if things always went
the way you wanted them to?
‐ Just remember,
don't screw with us.
We're not a bunch of idiots.
‐ [chuckles]
‐ I almost forgot,
Akabayashi wants to have
a little chat with you.
I know you're a busy guy,
but if you've got some time,
give him a ring.
‐ Yes, I'll make sure
and do that.
It's a point of pride with me,
making myself useful
to all my wonderful clients.
That's my job
as an info‐broker.
Well, it's more than just
a job.
It's my passion.
["Never Say Never"
by Three Lights Down Kings]
[man singing in Japanese]
♪ ♪
IZAYA: Do you know who
this young guy is?
No?
Would you like me to tell you?
[chuckles] Get ready
'cause it's a long story.
It goes all the way back to when
we were in middle school.
Next time,
"Eloquent and Competent."