[theme song playing]
[man singing in Japanese]
[screams]
It would be in your best
interest to come quietly.
As a matter of fact, I sent
Aoba and the rest of the guys
to attack
the Yellow Scarves today.
[Sloan]
Mother, I have captured Izaya.
[Kasane]
Would you please bring him
to Number Twelve's office?
You've got a penalty round
coming your way.
Bastard!
[singing resumes]
[music ends]
-[Celty] Uh...
-Long time no see!
-How you been?
-Walker? And, uh, driver guy?
-Hi, Celty.
-It's been awhile!
Well, not really, 'cause we
met up just the other day, huh?
I guess since me and Seiji
are together all day every day,
it feels like it's been forever
since I've seen anyone!
-[Emilia] Why did I buy these?
- [Celty] Seiji and Mika?
Even Namie Yagiri's here.
[Shingen]
Oh, hey there, Celty!
Took you long enough.
How dare you show
your face here!
-It's nice to meet you.
-Who the--?
Welcome home, Celty!
I missed you so much today!
You'd think having
all these people hanging out
would help kill the loneliness,
but they don't.
You're the only one
who can do that.
Thank you. You're sweet.
What's going on?
Why is everyone
in our apartment?
Yeah, funny story...
[Shinra narrating]
A storm is brewing.
A sword is drawn.
Nature convulses.
Chaos reigns and--
Oh, never mind.
The point is, once again,
something's brewing
in the city.
Something bad.
And caught in the middle is,
you guessed it.
Look, I already told you
I don't know her.
-[banging]
-[man] Cut the shit!
Three days ago, you busted up
her arm real good! Admit it!
Now, why the hell would I go
and do something like that?
You should be checking her out,
instead of giving me
the runaround.
[man]
Keep playing cool, tough guy!
Everyone's got their breaking
point, even a thug like you!
[scoffs]
I hear your little brother's
a big celebrity.
All it'd take is finding
a little dope on him
and his career goes
right in the shitter!
All right, if I did something
to piss you guys off--
You didn't piss us off.
We just want you off the streets
of Ikebukuro for a little while.
-That's all.
-Huh? The hell you say?
Did that goddamn flea
pay you off to--?
Oh, I get it. That sword's
got you under its spell--
It'd be easy for us
to hang a rap on you.
Me and my partner
could beat each other up
and say you did it.
I see.
-If that's how you want it.
-Huh?
Believe it or not, I have
a lot of respect for cops,
but you guys?
You're not cops anymore.
I'm going to enjoy
taking your asses apart!
-Who the hell--?
-Excuse me.
How's it going?
I hear you and the Headless
Rider are buddies.
Maybe I am, maybe I'm not.
Do me a favor if you are.
In the interests
of public safety,
tell it to turn
its goddamn headlight on.
And you can also tell it
to expect a ticket
for no license and no plates.
Could you do that for me,
big guy? Thanks.
-Have a nice day. Move.
-What the hell is this? [grunts]
You want to lose
your badge, officer?
I could hear you guys
down the hall,
talking all kinds of stupid.
I hate ratting out fellow cops,
but you'll be getting a visit
from one of my pals
in Internal Affairs.
-[groans, breathes heavily]
-[chuckles]
-What are you laughing at?
-Hmm.
Next time you see that cop,
you should thank him.
He's the reason
you're still alive.
Come again?
You heard me, guy.
Up until a minute ago,
I thought this place was full
of possessed dickheads like you.
Now, I know there's
some normal people left.
So, let's go.
Give me all you've got,
'cause I can take it.
[Shinra]
They say, patience is a virtue.
Good luck with that!
[Mikado]
Are you guys okay?
Oh, they're fine.
It takes more than a couple
scratches to get us down.
[growls] Where were you
when it was going down?
Yeah, Aoba!
You didn't do shit!
-Yeah!
-What? Listen, I--
Come on, guys! Stop fighting!
We're not really fighting.
Just messing around, is all.
It didn't look like it to me.
Wait. Didn't you say there was
someone who wanted to see me?
Yeah. He's downstairs.
[Shinra] Could it be another
member of the Dollars?
Or maybe it's someone who heard
about Mikado's big purge
and came by to say
they wanted to help.
It's okay!
You can let him up now.
I'm Shijima.
How's it going?
[Shinra]
Watch your back!
He's a schemer!
So? What about the guy
who ran Kadota down?
-You find out who did it yet?
-No.
And there's that Orihara prick.
I bet Shiki thinks Sloan
can keep him in line,
but I don't trust
that Russian son of a bitch.
Yeah.
I don't know
what kind of twisty shit
that info broker and your kid
brother are cooking up next,
but these Dollars smell
like an opportunity
to score some fast cash.
[chuckles]
[Shinra] Ooh, he's definitely
planning something sinister.
Scary!
Finally, we come back
to my better half: Celty.
So, here's what happened:
My stepmom came over
to clean the place,
and then Walker showed up.
He said something
about the apartment
being a cool place
for a secret base.
I didn't know
what he was talking about,
so I just let him ramble on.
Anyway, that's when
Seiji and Mika showed up,
looking for a place to crash
for a while.
Then, while I was asking
what they meant,
my dad came over
with Egor there.
I was listening to my dad
explain why they were here,
and that's about the time
you came home!
Someone tell me
what's going on!
Um, we're putting you out.
I think we'll go look
for another place to stay.
You always speak calmly
and clearly, no matter what.
So, let's have it. What are you
and Mika doing here?
Well, actually--
Take your dirty hands
off my Seiji, you no-good
miserable pig!
[growling]
Relax, Namie. It's plutonic.
Tell me why you're here.
-That's my business, not yours!
-[Shinra] Disorganized clutter.
A mix of the good and the bad.
[Mairu]
Hey, where is everybody?
[Kururi]
I know, right?
It's like, every time something
strange happens in town,
all the users in the chatroom
are off doing something else.
I don't like feeling lonely.
Come on, let's have fun!
-[dings]
-[Aoba]Hey there!
Oh, hello!
Thanks for joining us!
And just in time, too.
Our minds and bodies
were starting to ache
from loneliness.
It's a good thing you showed up
when you did, or else we'd--
Kururi, Mairu,
do you have a sec?
[Kururi] It must be serious,
if you don't want to discuss it
on the forum.
[Mairu]
What's up?
[Aoba] It's not
that big a deal, but...
you might want to stay away
from Ikebukuro for a while.
Things are getting
kind of hairy around here,
and there's a chance
your brother might
get caught up in it.
I have a feeling
there'll be people out,
looking for you guys.
It sounds to me
like you're mixed up
in whatever's going on
out there, too.
Scary!
[Kururi]
For the past few days,
I could feel something weird
was going on in the city.
I wonder if you're the one
behind it.
And behind Kyohei's
hit and run, too.
I'm in so deep now, whether
I did or didn't is irrelevant.
If anything, I'm glad
I got to know the two of you.
But, right now,
there's things happening
that I've sort of been
looking forward to.
And I want you to know that
if, after the dust settles,
you still want to be friends,
um, that'd make me... happy.
[man]
Hey, Sloan. What's going on?
[Sloan]
I think he fell down stair
and hit back of head.
I take to hospital.
-Maybe we should go with you.
-Nyet.
This, I can handle on own.
Nah, uh-uh.
For all we know, you could still
be working for the Awakusus.
You might drop him off
on their doorstep
and we wouldn't want that.
[groans]
-It's me.
-[car engine starts]
I think we got us a lead.
[slow footsteps]
-[man] Hold it right there!
-Huh?
-[gasps]
-[groans]
-[grunts]
That's not--
-I sense Saika.
-[laughs]
[Shingen]
I guess tailing Namie was
a good idea after all, eh?
Shingen... Kishitani...
[growls] What are you
standing around for? Get him!
[groans]
[body thuds]
What-- What do you think
you're doing?
[Shingen] I told you
this would happen. Remember?
"You leave me no choice,
now that you've hurt my boy,"
or something like that.
I said I'd smash
your goddamn face in
and here we are!
[Eijiro]
Crap. I didn't smash
his goddamn face in.
[Egor]
I don't think it matters.
[Shingen]
Now, it's my turn to ask you,
what do you think you're doing?
Nebula hasn't gotten
a single report from you
on any of your activities.
-[grunts]
-[Egor] Uh-oh. Shingen?
[Eijiro] We should get
while the getting's good.
[Shingen] Almost done,
Gas Mask Two and Three!
[gasps, groans]
-[Shingen] We'll meet again!
-[coughing]
And, when we do,
I hope you've had a chance
to bone up on your skills!
The Fiend with Three Masks
only accepts worthy opponents!
There it is, Shinra.
I gave the villain who hurt you
a good, sound clobbering.
Sure, I could've sued
the pants off that dirtbag,
but the last thing
you and Celty need
is the law sniffing around.
I think I handled him
pretty good.
I didn't go too overboard.
Actually, you sort of did.
Check out what was
on the news yesterday.
Looks like this has your dad
written all over it, Dr. K.
[man]
This afternoon,
in a residential area
in Shinjuku,
several smoke bombs
were detonated,
sending residents into a panic
and snarling traffic.
According to eyewitnesses,
three men in white lab coats
were seen fleeing the area
shortly after--
[Shingen]
Click! Click! Click!
Whoa! Easy, easy! Can't we talk
about this like adults?
[Egor]
Hold on a sec.
Celty, those were
my smoke grenades,
so I'm the one
you should be upset with.
I'm sorry. Who are you?
Where are my manners?
My name is Egor.
Simon and I go back many years.
Really?
Dr. K, your dad
is like the coolest dad
in the history of dads!
His gas mask is so dope!
Oh, dude, I just thought
of something.
What if when he takes it
off at night,
there's a hot girl underneath?
Hot girls with gravelly voices
do it for you?
My first wife, Shinra's mom,
she and I would
swap clothes sometimes.
True story!
It must be weird
hearing your dad blurt out
his kinks in public.
I love you, but don't ever
mention that again.
You want to try swapping clothes
with me sometime?
God, no. That's creepy.
Don't be such a copycat!
When Seiji was a little kid,
he used to wear my hand-me-down
pajamas all the time,
you thieving little bitch.
Hang on. I thought
those were boy pajamas.
No, I wore them once
and let the pants out
so they'd fit you!
-[Seiji] Oh.
-Ugh.
The only normal people here
are that Egor guy and...
whatever the driver's name is.
[Namie and Mika
continue bickering]
Excuse me, there's something
I want to say to you.
I have no intention
of lending an ear
to anything you have to say.
Oh, I'm sorry.
I meant, "lending an eye."
Woman, do you realize
you're in my house?
You stole my head
and I want it back!
[chuckles] Ask your boyfriend.
He did help me, after all.
Uh, could we talk
about this later?
Izaya Orihara has my head,
doesn't he?
Tell me now, or else!
Would you just tell her, sis?
I'd like to know, too.
Seiji!
[sighs]
All right, fine.
I had it the night
I ran away from you,
and I turned it over to Izaya.
-Happy?
-Seriously?
I can't tell you exactly
where it is, though,
because he doesn't keep it
in one place for long.
He'd bring it
to the office sometimes
and play catch with it,
like a ball.
Bastard! You don't treat
someone's head like that!
Who does he think he is?
I'll kill him.
Don't talk that way, Seiji.
You have too much to live for!
But if you really want him dead,
I'd gladly go to prison for you!
-What kind of big sister--
-Don't you dare lecture me!
You're the one playing house
with the unlicensed doctor
that hid your head!
Point taken.
But, just so you know,
he hasn't escaped my wrath.
If, by wrath, you mean
you smacked him once,
then fornicated
like a couple of animals,
I'm sure you showed him!
How did you know?
She's definitely
not an animal in bed.
She's more like a little bunny,
all timid and skit--
[choking]
This is not the type of stuff
we talk about
with company around!
[Shingen]
Hold on there, Celty!
What exactly do you
and my son do in bed?
-I'm asking as your doctor.
-You and your son are pervs!
Excuse me, but what's this
about your head?
Huh?
What? You mean,
your body is dating Dr. K here,
while at the same time,
your head is dating Izaya?
How's that possible?
My head and body
have separate minds,
and I promise you,
my head is not dating Izaya.
Not true. Izaya and your head
are madly in love.
Huh?
You'd be much better off
forgetting all about
that trashy flirt.
At night, all they do
is talk about how much
they love each other.
Her mouth coos, "Izaya, Izaya,"
while her body lies in bed with
Shinra, doing God knows what!
You're such a liar!
Oh, stop freaking out. You know
Izaya only cares about humans.
I bet he's playing catch
with it now.
Or maybe putting flowers in it,
like a vase or something.
You're not helping at all!
It makes no difference to me
if she's in love
with another man.
As long as I'm the last one
she smiles at, I'll be happy.
[sighs]
I hate hearing that, but your
obsessiveness is so attractive!
Don't worry, Seiji. If you want
smiles, I've got tons for you.
Shut up, you mangy alley cat!
Or I'll rip your damn skin off
and turn you into a shamisen!
Even if you did,
as long as I can make beautiful
sounds for Seiji, I'd be happy.
Seiji, you've got the potential
to be a true fan of the arts.
If you want, I could loan you
some really kinky doujinshi
about Dullahans and sexy demons
with expanding necks!
[Celty]
They make stuff like that?
Hey, would you mind
if I checked some of it out?
Especially the ones
about Dullahans!
Shinra!
You have nothing to worry about.
You know me.
I'm a one-Dullahan man.
But, like, maybe those stories
could give us some ideas
for when we-- [yelps]
Sorry, Celty! Ow!
Too tight! Too tight!
-[coughing] Ow!
-[gasps]
[groans]
Sorry, I shouldn't be so rough
with you. Are you okay?
Oh, yeah.
It's good physical therapy.
I see how it is, Celty.
Out in the world, you're
a no-nonsense kind of gal,
but, with Shinra,
you act all needy and helpless.
That's going in my non-human
report for Nebula.
-Hold it. Report?
-There's a non-human report?
Does it have
a centuries-old vampire
with a body
of a cheerleader in it?
[Walker] Or how about
a tsundere were-wolf?
There's a pedophile vampire,
who loves video games, in it.
There's also
a couple of shape-shifters,
who like to disguise themselves
as gorgeous girls.
Where have you been all my life?
This is great!
Listen, if you introduce me
to that vampire,
I'll sell you one half
of my soul!
Then, I can get her to bite me.
Then, I can use
my brand new vampire power
to find the guy
who ran Kyohei over
and beat the living shit
out of him!
[Shingen] I'm sorry
for whoever got run over,
but I can't introduce you.
That's confidential. I'd get
my credentials taken away.
Stop making things
more complicated!
So, I guess this means
you're a spy for the Awakusus.
Not exactly, but you are
in right ball park, malyshka!
[grunts]
-[electricity crackling]
-[groans]
He's not as tough as he looks.
He was acting weird,
like someone was controlling
him, or something.
That's why he went down so easy.
[Mikage]
You get a look at his eyes?
They looked the same
as those guys Haruna took out.
Do you think maybe
she turned traitor on Izaya?
I don't know about that. I ran
a check on this house, though,
and it definitely doesn't belong
to the Awakusu Group.
What do you think's
going on, Izaya? Get up.
Well, that was fun
while it lasted.
So, when did you realize
I wasn't really unconscious,
Mr. Kine?
When Mikage hauled off
and gave you that kick.
I could totally see you
grit your teeth.
Yeah, that took me completely
by surprise.
You should be thankful
I didn't put all I had into it.
-You're right. Thank you.
-Well?
Sloan was acting
under the influence of Saika.
However, neither Anri
nor Haruna were behind it.
It was someone else:
Kasane Kujiragi.
She's yet another wielder
of Saika.
Can you believe our luck?
The second
we declare war on her,
we manage to find
one of her hideouts.
Not too shabby.
[chuckles]
Here's an idea.
Let's wait for her
to come home.
We'll throw her
a surprise party!
[Celty] All right,
let me get this straight.
Walker, you,
and whats-his-name the driver
were looking for the person
who ran Kyohei over
and some whacko attacked you.
Mm-hmm.
Then, you guys decided to stop
here and lay low for a while.
After all this time,
you still don't know my name?
[Walker]
Mmm?
-I don't.
-Jeez, it's Saburo! Sa-bu-ro.
Right. Sorry.
As for you, Namie,
you say your uncle's
after my head,
and he and the secretary
of some guy called Yodogiri
tried to kidnap you.
Seiji and Mika,
you guys got tipped off
that someone wanted
to kidnap you, too.
Actually, Mika was the one
who found out.
Yeah, I bugged
Yagiri Pharmaceuticals
and overheard someone
talking about it.
-I was so scared.
-[Celty] I can imagine.
And tonight, I found out
Izaya's an even bigger bastard
than I thought.
I'll beat him senseless
and get my head back!
-But, Celty...
-Don't worry.
I'll figure out a way to get it
without actually touching it.
Then, I'll give it
to your dad to hold onto.
I don't care
if he uses it for research.
It's going to be a long time
before I take it back. Decades.
And I'll only take it back
after you're gone.
-Thank you.
-[Emilia] Okie-dokie, then!
As a representative
of the Nebula Corporation,
I promise your donation will be
treated with the utmost care.
The board might have
other ideas, pumpkin.
Don't be such a worry-wart!
A little sweet-talk and those
suckers will fall for anything!
I wonder who the bigger sucker
is: Me or the company?
Okay, Namie,
what's Izaya planning next?
I'm not obligated
to tell you anything.
Scratch that,
I'll tell you something
that'll make your blood boil.
The pervert in the mask knew
Izaya had your head.
He's known this whole time.
[Shingen]
You think maybe you could've
saved that revelation for,
oh, I don't know,
a more appropriate occasion?
I'm too tired to play
these games anymore.
-Besides...
-Hmm?
I'm stuck in a weird spot now.
Should I tell them
what's going down
between the Dollars
and the Yellow Scarves?
I don't know.
[Shinra narrating]
Trouble's brewing in Ikebukuro,
and smack-dab
in the middle of it,
are the Dollars and Celty.
You guys,
I think I have an idea.
Let's team up. You know,
join forces and stuff!
-Well? What do you think?
-What, and be like the Dollars?
Uh-uh, I was thinking
we could all pool our resources
and share information.
Mmm, I guess kind of
like a guild?
I love it! A guild!
Swords, dragons, fantasy!
Next, we should appoint
a leader.
How about it, Celty?
-Want to be our leader?
-What?
It's not like you'll have
to give orders or anything.
You'll be the person
everyone reports to. Sound good?
Wait, report to me? Why me?
What are you talking about?
Think about it, Celty. You're
tied in to the whole city.
We can come to you
with whatever info we find,
and you can be the one
to make sense of it all.
Is everyone okay with this?
[Shinra]
The woman I love is caught up
in something big,
and I'm going to help
get her out.
Don't worry, Celty.
I'll be here to help you.
All right.
If everyone's fine with it,
so am I.
[chuckles]
Ladies and gentlemen,
we're a guild!
[Shinra]
And now, as a team,
we have a chance
to get to the person
who's responsible
for all of our troubles.
Whoever it is,
we're going to get them.
Count on it!
[theme song playing]
[Shingen]
Let's talk about women
for a second.
All kinds of women.
Suffering women,
powerful women,
warrior women,
sneaky, conniving women.
Next time: Bell the Cat.
Women will be women.