♪ [man singing in Japanese]
[Celty]
Saika?
[Kasane] I'm surprised
to be saying this,
but I'm feeling
rather jealous.
Let me guess. Something
happened to Celty, didn't it?
All right, then. Let's go!
♪ [continues]
[Izaya] Remember this
from science class?
A few drops of acidic liquid
turns litmus paper red,
while alkaline turns it blue.
You try all kinds of liquids,
but you eventually get bored
because the paper only
reacts one of two ways.
Humans, though, react in
millions of different ways.
-Huh.
-Humans are never boring.
[chuckle]
How fun.
-Let's go.
-Where to?
To meet a certain someone
who just might provide
the challenge
you've been hoping for.
Hmm?
Unlike litmus paper,
if you put a drop
of something on a human,
the reaction is wildly
unpredictable.
Case in point, these boys.
So, Mikado, what did you
and my brother talk about?
Mm, this and that.
He asked if you were okay
and that I watch your back.
[scoff]
You gotta be kidding me.
He doesn't care.
I wish I had a brother
like you.
You know,
I was an only child.
Yeah, and you were lucky.
Trust me, you're better off
not having a brother like mine.
Look, I asked you a question.
So let's have it.
I know my brother didn't
come here just to chat.
Could you give me a sec?
I just have to finish
checking the boards,
and then--
-Ohh.
-What? What's going on?
Oh, shit.
[typing]
Good evening.
[Namie]
There you are, Mikado.
Sorry. You have
the wrong person.
My name is Tanaka.
What do you think you're doing?
Oh, shut up!
Go find Kasane Kujiragi
and Shinra Kishitani.
And Seitaro Yagiri, the man
behind all these problems.
Round up the Dollars and
destroy him like you did me.
[Kururi] Looks like this
chat's about to get heavy.
[Mairu]
Epic suck.
I don't know what
you're talking about.
Who is this Kujiragi person?
What are you up to?
[grumble]
If anyone's up
to something, it's you.
How can you not see
what's going on around you?
All I want
is to end this mess.
I need you to do that.
You're involved in
everything bad going on,
but you don't have a clue.
Well, I'm going to
bring you up to speed
because that's the only
way we can end this.
-Please stop.
-Uh-oh, this is getting tense.
Something tells me it'll be
better if I log out right now.
I wonder if this
is what Jyunsui 100%
was talking about before.
I wonder if Aoba's okay.
Why did they mention
your name?
Uh--
[gasp]
Please don't. You can't
dox people like that.
I'll do whatever I have to,
to put an end to this.
-[scoffs]
-[Izaya] Yes, ma'am.
Now that's what I call
being human.
Some would say unhinged,
emotional people like you
should stay away
from blogs and chat rooms.
But what do they know?
Your reaction
is absolutely human.
[Namie]
Remember those Slasher attacks?
Would you like to know how
she was involved with those?
She's giving up personal
info left and right.
This chat's
like those notebooks
you find in arcades,
where players scribble
down nasty things
about other players.
-Scary.
-[typing]
That's enough.
Please stop.
-You'll destroy everything.
-[typing]
Everything was destroyed
a long time ago.
And you did it, remember?
The same night you
destroyed my research.
-Stop!
-Come back.
-I'd run away, too.
-I'm so scared.
You can't ignore this, Mikado.
Remember what you told me?
How you wanted
to see real life have
a happy ending?
After all that sanctimonious
talk, you ruined my life.
Don't forget that.
Take responsibility
for what you said.
Uh--Uh--Uh...
And we're back
with another update.
At this point,
details of the attack
are still sketchy,
but police have confirmed
the evidence from
the squad car is missing.
-Huh?
-They also confirmed
the explosion was caused
by a grenade fired from
some type of heavy rifle.
Currently, the suspect
is believed to be
hiding somewhere
in the city.
The MPD has deployed dozens
of officers throughout Tokyo
to search for the suspect,
but they have no leads
and are asking the public
for help.
Jesus. What the hell's
going on?
The advent
of Demon City Ikebukuro
is upon us, that's what!
Soon, a demon-summoning app
will download itself
onto my phone,
and our new life
in the apocalypse begins!
Let's survive!
[shouting]
-[crash]
-Uhh!
-[laughing]
-Huh?
[pounding]
-[Walker] This is gonna
be so rad! I can't wait!
-Oh, brother.
Am I the only normal
person here? This sucks.
-[ringtone]
-Hmm?
Togucchan, it's me.
It's about Dotachin.
-Oh, my God! Oh, my God!
-Chill out! What's going on
with Kyohei?
You know how the doctors
all said he wouldn't be able
to walk for a while?
He left a note
and he snuck outta here.
-Crap.
-What do we do?
I bet--I bet he's
out there right now
looking for the guy
that ran him over.
-Oh.
-Huh?
By the way,
you mentioned
some chick called Anri
a couple of times.
Her last name Sonohara?
Wait. You know her, too?
Cute girl with glasses?
Insanely huge rack
for her size?
Yeah. That's her.
She was at the hospital today
with a chick called
Eri-something or other.
Who's Eri?
She's got, like,
dark hair, a hat, cute.
Last name's Karisawa.
That's Erika.
How do you know her and Anri?
I'll tell you about it later.
Let's get you face-to-face
with Mikado.
Or maybe you should
talk to Anri first.
I don't know.
Actually, it's better
if I keep her in the dark
about stuff a little longer.
As soon as I settle up
with Mikado,
things will be cool
and we'll both go see her.
You're making a mistake
not talking to her.
In my experience,
don't ever sell a lady short.
-What?
-Thing about chicks is,
they're way tougher
and way smarter than us guys.
We can sneak around
all we want,
but they always
got our number.
That's guaranteed.
Hell, I don't even try
to hide my cheating
from my honeys.
It's amazing you still
got honeys to cheat on.
If you want to keep her
out of the loop and shit,
that's up to you,
but be careful.
Chicks know when a guy's
hiding something,
and these days,
it's a piece of cake
for them to find out what.
Uh--
[Izaya]
Humans have infinite reactions,
but their bodies
have limitations.
For example, if they fall
from a tall building,
-they'll die.
-[horse neighs]
A monster, on the other hand,
would survive the same fall.
That doesn't sound fair,
now does it?
You know,
on second thought,
I better call her
just in case.
Okay. How far is
her place from here?
It's not too far.
A little bit of a walk,
but not too bad.
Hi, Celty?
Um, this is Anri.
Can I come over
and see you now?
Please call back and let me
know if this is a good time.
Talk to you soon. Bye.
I left a message,
but we should start
heading over.
Come on. [gasp]
[noise]
You want to go where that
noise is coming from, huh?
[ring]
I figured.
Maybe I can climb
that building.
Hmm?
Uh-huh.
Whatever happened to Celty,
Team Red-eye's behind it.
They ain't working
for the city,
so let's bust through 'em.
[neigh]
Nice work.
And by the way,
I had no idea you were
a Saika wielder.
That said,
is it safe like that?
I can keep it
under control from here.
Although,
if I were to walk away,
it would most likely return
to its sword form.
Then, do I just take
the body and sword, and go?
Have you ever had to deal
with an unrestrained
Dullahan before?
If so, you're more than welcome
to do as you wish.
Hmm. You can handle it.
That would be for the best.
Well, the head should
be here any minute now.
Oh?
Once it reunites with its body,
it will settle down,
and then it will return
to its original form.
When it does,
I shall use Saika
to sever the head
from the body again.
Then, we can claim
the body for ourselves.
Are you sure
it'll calm down, though?
The Dullahan's head contains
its memories from before.
If the body regains
those memories,
it should revert
to its former self.
As for its memories
as the Headless Rider,
I'm not sure if those
will transfer over.
That could be good.
I bet without them,
that thing'll be a hell
of a lot easier to handle.
Not remembering her life
as the Headless Rider
would be preferable
for me as well.
Why do you say that?
It would also be
convenient for me
if my rival in love
lost her memories.
Rival?
[man]
Hey! Boss!
What?
You got the head with you?
No, sir. There's a psycho
coming down the alley.
-[panting]
-[neigh]
[neigh]
Now what?
Oh, God, it's coming!
What's coming?
Get your ass back here!
[bike bell rings]
[Izaya] I wondered why
Saika-zombies would be
blocking the street,
and there's the reason.
[chuckle]
This is too good to be true.
What kind of quote-unquote
liquid should I drop on them?
[screaming]
Shizu-chan.
Uh, Ms. Kujiragi,
do you know him?
The man is Shizuo Heiwajima.
The bike is a Cóiste Bodhar.
As far as I know,
the man's a normal human
with inhuman strength.
-[neigh]
-Whoa!
What the hell
did you stop for?
-Is that Celty?
-[bike bell rings]
All right, what did
you guys do to Celty?
I can answer that.
The swirling mass above
was once the entity
you and your friends
referred to as Celty Sturluson.
As you can see, she's now
a rampaging monster.
What the hell
are you people after anyway?
She--or, rather,
what she used to be--
is, in my opinion, nothing more
than a product to be sold.
You don't have
to tell him all that.
There's no point in keeping it
a secret from him.
She's not human
or a protected species.
She's a monster.
Hunting and selling such things
is my line of business.
[gasp]
Yeah. She's right.
All this is, is business.
It's not illegal.
Besides,
if you think about it,
monsters aren't even
supposed to exist anyway.
You got a point there.
I guess I can see where
you guys are coming from.
I appreciate
your understanding.
Whatever. I don't care
if it's legal or not.
She's Celty. And she's one
of my best friends, lady.
And seeing her like that,
being treated
like your merchandise...
You think I'm gonna stand here
and watch her suffer?
Oof!
Don't let him kill me!
Let me handle this.
You say she is one
of your friends, correct?
Look at what she has become.
Are you sure you can still
call Celty Sturluson
your friend?
Damn straight I can.
Oh, really? There's nothing
human about it anymore.
How can you call
a raging monster your friend?
Look, lady, ever since
I was a little kid,
there ain't been a day
when I haven't been
called a monster.
I know what it's like
to lose my shit, too.
But sometimes Celty was
there to talk me down,
and I was lucky she was,
real lucky.
She saved my ass just by
giving a damn about me.
I owe her.
So now it's my turn
to save her ass.
Huh.
Let go, lady.
I ain't saying it twice.
-Please, hear me out.
-Huh?
I envy you
and Celty Sturluson.
I never had anyone
in my life
who cared about me.
[bike bell rings]
Don't worry, pal.
I'll go get Celty right now.
[gun cocks]
[Varona]
I would not if were you.
Holy shit.
This chat room's messed up.
It's not always
this crazy.
"Yagiri." Is Seiji
mixed up in this?
[gasp]
Varona.
I request you to stand down
and to not resist, please,
for your sake.
Whatcha pointing that
at me for?
Better not be real.
It is most certainly
for real,
and I will use
if you do not comply.
Mind telling me
what you're doing here?
I am working. But is not
for our loan collection job.
She is new client,
and if harm her,
I will take action.
There's no law against
having a second gig,
but there's better ones
out there.
All right. You win.
Just chill with the gun.
I must keep you covered
until job complete
and I make confession to you.
[sigh]
What?
At end of April,
on school ground
in Toshima Ward,
you were attacked by person
wearing full-face
motorcycle helmet.
This person try stabbing you
with Spetsnaz combat knife.
Oh, yeah. Her.
You're gonna say
it was you, right?
-Mm.
-Come on.
Give me some credit.
I ain't that dumb.
You're wearing
the same thing now
you did then.
I can't say
I was always sure.
-But I was--
-Aware of possibility?
That is unacceptable answer.
It is not like you.
If there was hint
I was attacker,
you would have acted.
Or else, why did you not
crush my cervical vertebrae
when you had chance?
'Cause I like having you around
and hearing you talk, too.
Besides,
we've been working
together for a while,
I'm not gonna go
busting up my trainee.
Your statement conflict
with personality.
-Please explain.
-All right, look,
I only beat down the things
that don't make sense to me.
But if I understand
where someone's coming from,
it don't matter
if I get shot or stabbed.
I wouldn't get pissed.
So now what?
The ball's
in your court, Varona.
You're my trainee.
You want to talk,
that's what I'm here for.
I want...
[thinking]
What is it I want?
I want to destroy Shizuo.
And I want to see
how powerful humans are.
I cannot destroy him
with gun.
There is no point unless
we fight on equal footing,
without restraint.
Hey, what are you doing
standing there?
Hurry up and shoot
that bastard already!
Yo, fat boy.
Didn't you hear?
I get pissed off when
things don't make sense.
[gasp]
If you try
and kill someone,
you gotta be ready
to get killed yourself.
That's how it works.
So, if you're telling
Varona to kill me,
and that is
what you're doing,
it's the same as telling her
to get ready to die
if things work out that way.
Bastard. She happens
to be my trainee.
You're not telling my trainee
to risk her life
for you, are ya? Huh?
[whimpering]
W-Wait a second.
L-Let's work this out.
You do realize you are not
under the employ
of Mr. Yagiri.
You are under no obligation
to follow his orders.
-Mm.
-If one brings their personal
feelings into their work,
it will lead to less
than desirable results.
We are both guilty of that.
I suggest
we leave for tonight
and reflect on our error.
Wh-What are you talking about?
You can't leave.
Do something.
This guy's gonna kill me!
I am sorry. However, there
is no clause in our contract
that states I'm required
to protect you.
-What?
-As promised,
I have delivered one
of the products to you.
As for the body
of the Dullahan and Saika,
I shall bring them to you
another day.
-W-Wait. You can't--
-I don't want to die today.
Come back! Is it the money?
L-Let's work it out!
You don't know
when to shut up, tubby.
Scrape up your goon
and beat it
before I kick your ass,
unless you want
your ass kicked. Well?
-[thinking]
Construction? This late?
-No? I mean no!
Shizuo!
-Jesus. I'm going home.
-Varona!
Varona.
Come on, can you hear me?
Wake up.
I am awake, Shizuo.
Thank God.
Can you get up? Or--
Do not worry for me.
I was not planning for this.
But I could not avoid
falling debris in time.
You idiot. Don't go risking
your life for a guy like me.
Look, Shizuo!
Izaya.
[gasping]
You okay?
Yeah, I guess you are.
-[grunt]
-[knuckles crack]
Sorry, but I'm about
to do something stupid.
And if you want to stab me
or shoot me for doing it,
I won't complain.
You risked your life
to save me,
and here I go blowing it.
When Celty gets
back to normal,
you can kick my ass
all you want.
You got my word.
Shizuo, come back.
[phone rings]
-What?
-[Izaya] Hey, Shizu-chan.
I can't believe
that didn't kill you.
I guess you really
are a monster.
It was kind of funny
watching you save
a human, though.
How very un-monster-y.
I might have
mentioned this before,
but I think you save people
to make them like you.
Or, in this case,
I think you saved Varona
because you like her.
You're not going to leave
Celty like that, are you?
And how could you
let Kujiragi go?
You know,
that woman is evil.
-Izaya
-What?
So long.
Yes. Goodbye.
♪ [singing in Japanese]
[Tom]
No matter what happens,
just keep your cool.
That's always been my motto,
but I get the feeling
I'm about to get dragged
into some heavy shit.
Next time: A Tiger Dies
and Leaves His Skin.
I just want my old life back.
That asking too much?