["Day You Laugh"
by Toyonaga Toshiyuki]
♪ ♪
[man singing in Japanese]
‐ How could this city
leave me behind?
The truth is I never caught up
with it in the first place.
‐ [screams]
‐ [gasps]
‐ This bloody piece of paper
is our contract.
MAN: It's really an honor,
Miss Hijiribe.
YUHEI: The serial killer
they call Hollywood in the news,
that's you, isn't it?
SHIKI: You didn't happen to
examine Ruri Hijiribe.
MAN: Do you know about
that serial killer, Hollywood?
[man singing in Japanese]
♪ ♪
‐ [chuckles]
[gentle music]
ANRI: It's summer now,
and the sky's changed color.
The person I was before
wouldn't have noticed
something like that.
If I look around, it doesn't
seem like anything's changed,
but I know everything has.
When I fought that lady
at school,
I was scared.
Scared that Mikado
might have seen me,
but he hasn't brought it up,
and I haven't had a chance
to talk to him about it yet.
It's like nothing's changed,
in that sense anyway.
‐ Hey, Anri, ready for summer?
‐ Yeah, I guess so.
‐ It's kind of a drag,
making us reps meet
before letting us go, huh?
Do you have any plans
for the summer break?
‐ Huh?
Oh, uh, no.
I didn't make any plans.
‐ That sucks.
Well, if you get bored
or something,
give me a call.
‐ Yeah, sure.
‐ Great. You coming?
ANRI: Still,
something's different.
But what's different and how?
I still don't get
what it could be.
I can't put it into words.
‐ Hi, Mom. How's it going?
My brother's out?
You don't say.
Hm.
ANRI: Even the city
looks different now.
But different in ways that are
too subtle to point out.
KYO: I'm so in love
with Yuhei.
He's my inspiration.
My reason for waking up
in the morning.
I love him!
SAN: Scary.
SETTON: It sounds like you have
an unhealthy obsession.
BAKYURA: I heard Yuhei Hanejima
and Ruri Hijiribe
are lovers now.
And I also heard Ruri's got
her own stalker, too.
SAIKA: A stalker?
SAN: Dollars.
SETTON: Huh?
BAKYURA: What'd you bring up
the Dollars for?
KYO: I'm sorry
about that, guys.
San jumped the gun
a little bit there.
See, the rumor
going around town
is Ruri Hijiribe's stalker might
be a member of the Dollars.
SETTON: Really?
Is that right?
SAN: Scary.
‐ What's going on, fellas?
There something
I can do for you?
‐ As a matter of fact,
yeah, there is, fella.
‐ Know who we are, huh?
You ever hear of
a gang called the Dollars?
‐ We're collecting donations
for our health plan,
and we'd appreciate
anything you can give.
‐ Yeah.
‐ [whimpers, laughs]
[laughter]
‐ Huh?
‐ What the‐‐
‐ Uh...
KYO: I've got another rumor
about the Dollars for you.
I hear there's some infighting
going on in the gang.
‐ What do you dipshits want?
‐ There's nothing to see here.
Go on, beat it.
‐ What a coincidence,
we're in the Dollars, too.
Mind if we give you a hand?
‐ Huh?
‐ No, you can't!
Why should we cut you guys in
on our score?
We were here first,
so get out of here!
‐ Sorry, man,
you got the wrong idea.
I was talking to the old guy
back there.
‐ Huh?
‐ What?
Get the hell
out of here before‐‐
[thud]
You‐‐
I'm gonna kick your‐‐
[laughter]
‐ Here's what's gonna happen.
You're gonna give us
your phones,
and we're gonna cancel your
membership with the Dollars.
‐ You know it.
‐ And those orders
come straight from the top,
fella.
KYO: They say this new group
is pretty vicious,
and they have one thing
that sets them apart
from everyone else.
Whenever they attack,
they wear blue ski masks.
The masks have a pattern on them
that looks like shark teeth.
Shark teeth!
BAKYURA: Huh?
Really?
KYO: Yeah.
You hear about that before?
There was a gang in Ikebukuro
that called themselves
the Blue Squares,
and they wore
the same kind of masks.
BAKYURA: Oh. I didn't know that.
That's so weird!
[soft thuds]
‐ So what do you think
of Akane?
You think
she's got potential?
She seems like she does.
‐ Who the hell knows?
That's stuff's totally
up to her.
Her body's got potential though.
‐ For a teacher of martial arts,
you don't seem all that
motivated to teach,
and that last comment
is kind of sleazy.
‐ How's about I teach you
how to knock smart‐ass chicks
out of their gis
with one kick?
‐ Ooh, kinky,
but you're not pervy enough
to follow through with it.
‐ That's right, 'cause
Mikage would bust my balls.
Ugh.
‐ [chuckles]
[soft thuds]
Those are some focused hits.
Who's up there?
‐ Adabashi, I'd bet.
‐ Oh, he's that skeezy‐looking
guy, isn't he?
‐ You know it.
He started coming here
a while ago.
He's dangerous,
so leave him alone.
‐ Dangerous, huh?
Is he strong?
Stronger than Coach Mikage?
Stronger than you?
‐ No way, I can wipe the floor
with him anytime.
‐ Oh, come on.
Then how come I have
to stay away from him?
‐ Like that's a bad thing.
Look, I don't know
how strong he is.
I'm just going off
the vibe he's giving off.
It doesn't seem
like he's training
'cause he wants
to get stronger or anything.
It's like, I don't know,
like a feeling I get from him.
Gives me the creeps.
[coughing]
[laughs]
SETTON: Hey, I just realized,
Kanra hasn't logged on
in a while.
I bet he'd know
a few rumors, too.
KYO: He's probably busy
or something.
I'm sure he'll pop up again
one of these days.
Anyway, without him around,
this chat room's kinda dead,
don't you think?
Hey, San and I can go see if
any of our friends are around.
Maybe they'll join.
SETTON: You know,
that's a great idea.
I'll ask some of my friends
to log on, too.
BAKYURA: I'll hit up some of
mine, too. Party!
SAIKA: Me too.
[intense music]
♪ ♪
‐ Thank you so much,
transporter.
‐ You're welcome.
[Cóiste‐Bodhar neighs]
♪ ♪
[laughs]
[yelps]
‐ Welcome home, Celty.
[gasps]
‐ I'm safe.
I made it home.
Thank God.
‐ What's wrong?
What happened?
‐ I brought down
a chopper tonight.
But no matter how many shadows
I threw at the biker cop,
he dodged them all.
I was scared, so scared.
By the way, that girl's
pet snake is fine.
You know what she calls it?
Hakujoshi.
Can you believe that?
‐ I have no idea
what you're talking about.
You're safe now, though.
By the way, there's someone
here to see you.
‐ Hmm?
‐ I was out on one of
my house calls and ran into her.
She said she needs your advice
about something.
‐ Yo, what's up, party people?
‐ Well, look what
the cat dragged in.
Shizuo,
you've got some visitors.
‐ Huh?
‐ He never has visitors.
This is weird.
‐ It is complaints, perhaps.
Could be owner of forklift
he destroyed three days ago.
‐ No way, the boss took care of
that after I told him about it.
Wait, I bet it's about
that traffic mirror
from this morning.
‐ Ooh.
Huh?
‐ Oh.
‐ Sorry.
‐ Hey, how's it going, Kasuka?
Didn't expect to see you here.
‐ The receptionist told me
I should wait till you got back.
Is this a good time?
‐ Sure, I'm done
for the day anyway.
‐ I need your advice
about something.
‐ Seriously?
‐ Hi, it's, um,
nice to meet you.
‐ Holy shit!
We got Ruri Hijiribe
up in here!
‐ So it seems.
[all gasping]
‐ I knew it was her!
‐ Oh, my God!
‐ Hey, you jagoffs,
get back to work!
‐ I guess she goes
for the big blond type.
‐ Oh, that's where
I've seen you.
Are you and her, you know...
‐ Romantically involved.
But that's not‐‐
‐ Oh, great.
Good for you.
‐ [whimpers]
‐ Why are you shaking?
Are you cold?
‐ She's just a little nervous
because she saw one of your
rampages up close.
‐ [stammers]
‐ Actually...
‐ Oh, no, if I tell him
I was the one he attacked
with that bench, he'll know
my horrible secret.
‐ On second thought,
it doesn't matter.
I'm sorry you had to see that.
‐ What?
No, not at all.
If anyone's sorry, it's me.
‐ Hmm.
Oh, now I know
why you're here.
It's obvious.
You're getting hitched.
Well, I guess
the first order of business
should be telling
Mom and Dad about it.
After that, you guys are gonna
have to figure out
how to break it to your fans.
Got to be careful
how you do it.
The news could cause a riot.
‐ Thanks, but we're not
getting married.
I need your advice
about something else.
‐ What?
‐ The Dollars.
Do you know
anything about them?
‐ Oh, thank you.
I hope it's not a problem
showing up out of the blue
like this.
‐ Don't worry about it.
Shinra is so pushy, I'm sure
you didn't have a choice.
‐ What do you mean, I'm pushy?
That's not nice‐‐
‐ Well, how can I help you?
‐ Right.
Um, it's like Mikado isn't
himself lately.
‐ Is something wrong with him?
‐ I don't‐‐
I don't really know
how to describe
what's up with him.
It's just he's been acting
kind of strange, is all.
‐ Is he depressed?
‐ No, he seems happier
than ever.
I haven't seen him this cheerful
in a really long time.
He's like‐‐like he was
when Masaomi was here.
‐ This stalker of hers
is in the Dollars?
‐ I dug around,
and that's what it seems.
I also found out you're in it.
That's why I came here,
to see if you could help
put an end to this.
‐ Yeah, well, I don't know.
You see, I'm not
in the Dollars anymore,
and even when I was,
I didn't know what they were
or who was in it.
‐ Oh.
‐ What about the cops?
Did you talk to them?
‐ [whimpers]
Yes, I called them one night
when I couldn't unlock
my front door.
The stalker jammed something
in the keyhole.
‐ They checked the security
footage, every camera.
They said there was
a sketchy‐looking guy
in the hallway outside her door,
but they couldn't see his face.
‐ The police patrolled
the area after that,
but the guy showed up
at my photo shoot.
He left behind a bunch
of bloody pictures of me.
‐ If he knows where you work,
then that narrows
the list of suspects down.
Do you think maybe
he's someone you work with?
‐ It isn't.
The police checked.
They think he might be a fan.
Someone tied with a group
that deals info
about idols online.
‐ I've had scary fans
like that before,
and the police checked
all the ones
who were on my blacklist,
but they all had alibis.
‐ After snooping around,
I found out
the people trading info on Ruri
are in the Dollars.
I tried to register
to check it out,
but the Dollars are such
a tight community
they don't let anyone new in
unless you have an invitation.
‐ Oh, I'm sorry, man.
I don't have the brains to
be a hacker, that's for sure.
And if I only knew more
about the Dollars,
maybe that'd
help you somehow.
There's got to be someone
out there who does, but who?
[cat meows]
Huh?
‐ Hey there, Dokusonmaru.
Are you awake?
Ruri's going to be staying
at my place
until the police
catch this maniac.
‐ Huh?
‐ We don't want to leave
Dokusonmaru alone there, because
the stalker might hurt him.
Would you look after him for us?
It'll just be until
the police can catch the guy.
‐ Today we were walking
home from school together.
We said bye and then‐‐
‐ Hey, Anri.
‐ Yes, what?
‐ I know there are things
you don't want to tell me,
and it's okay if you don't.
I doubt I know how to fix
whatever's bugging you,
but no matter what that is
or what you're hiding,
I know I can work things out
so there's a spot for you.
‐ Uh.
‐ You'll see.
I'll fix everything so Masaomi
can come back here too.
All our friends will have
a place here.
Don't worry about a thing, Anri.
‐ He always said Masaomi would
come back to the city someday,
and now he says
he'll fix it so he can.
It's such a weird thing
for him to say.
‐ I think I get it.
Instead of trusting
his friend will come back,
he's putting his faith in his
own power to make it happen.
‐ You're right, that doesn't
sound like Mikado.
‐ Hm.
No.
‐ What really went down
at that factory?
It was right after that night
the kid showed up
out of the blue.
‐ It's about time...
‐ He certainly didn't act
like he wanted to be friends.
How did you get this address?
‐ Hey, it's okay.
Don't worry.
As long as we're cool,
I won't tell the cops
where you guys live.
I did tell my friends I was
coming here tonight though.
So if I do happen to disappear,
the cops would
definitely show up.
Or maybe a fire will break out.
Who knows?
‐ Huh, you sound like
Izaya Orihara.
‐ [gasps]
I never thought I'd
be compared to that asshole.
‐ Huh, so you do know
Izaya after all.
You guys are totally cut
from the same cloth.
I'd bet you're just like him,
never happy unless you have
the world in the palm
of your hand.
Like a couple of
greedy little boys.
You know what I want
in my hand?
Celty's, and I'll do anything
to keep her safe.
‐ Stop it, Shinra.
It would be stupid to kill him
over a few vague threats.
‐ Celty.
‐ No reason to get ahead
of ourselves, Doc.
For now, all I want from you
is one email addy.
Give me that,
and I'll leave you alone.
‐ We gave him
that email address,
but we haven't heard
from him since,
and that's got me worried.
Do you know who Mikado
associates with at school?
‐ Huh?
‐ Have you noticed him being
extra chummy with anyone?
‐ Let's see,
he's been hanging out a lot
with a younger boy called Aoba.
They're in the same committee
at school.
Thank you for talking to me.
I really appreciate it.
‐ No worries,
but it's gotten pretty late.
If you want,
you can spend the night.
‐ Oh, thank you,
but I couldn't impose on you
like that, really.
[doorbell chimes]
‐ Hmm?
[both chuckle]
[meows]
ANRI: I felt a lot better
after talking to them.
It definitely helped
calm me down.
And then I thought
if he really did change,
what could I do to help get him
back to the way he was?
‐ Hey, Saki.
‐ You're going
to Ikebukuro, huh?
‐ Are you psychic?
I gave myself a headache
thinking about
how to break it to you.
‐ I knew 'cause you've been
reading all those chat logs.
‐ [sighs]
One of them had a rumor
about there being Blue Squares
in the Dollars.
I'm worried they're planning
on taking over the Dollars,
like how the Yellow Scarves
tried.
I can't ignore that.
‐ Why do you want
to get involved?
Is it for a friend?
‐ Yeah, that's part of it.
There's also a score
I have to settle.
‐ I know it won't do any good
to tell you not to go,
but it's dangerous,
and I don't want you
to get hurt.
‐ Well, that's not fair.
A good girlfriend would
keep that stuff to herself.
‐ I don't care
if it's fair or not.
I'm the one
who has to sit here, waiting.
‐ For me to come back?
‐ For you to crack
those stupid jokes and laugh
and be a dork,
like you used to.
‐ That's definitely not fair.
‐ Huh?
‐ Listen, it's like
I have to go back there,
'cause there's a whole bunch
of people I want you to meet.
They're my friends, and I want
them to meet you, too.
ANRI: It's natural
for this city
and everyone who lives in it
to change.
So why should I want
to stop that from happening?
Do I want things to go back
to the way they were?
‐ Thank God. I'm glad
none of you guys got hurt.
Whatever you do,
try and be careful out there.
‐ They'll be okay,
but check this out.
Ruri Hijiribe's stalker
might be a Dollar.
You hear about that?
‐ Yeah, that's a problem.
We should move on it.
That's the kind of member
the Dollars don't need.
[chime]
GAKI: Nice to meet you.
I look forward to chatting if
anyone ever decides to log on.
Sumiuta‐‐I mean, Saika
sent me an invite,
so here I am.
SHARO: Hello there.
GAKI: Hello.
Nice to meet you.
Do you come to this board often?
SHARO: Nope, I just joined.
I also got an invite
from a friend.
We're the only ones here.
I wonder where the regulars are.
PURE WATER 100%: Hey, guys!
I've been lurking this board
up till now.
Do you mind if I join in?
A friend sent me an invite,
but I've never done this before.
Anyway, nice to meet you.
SAKI: Hi, everyone.
Bakyura sent me an invitation.
My name's Saki.
Nice to meet you.
SHARO: Good evening.
PURE WATER 100%: Evening!
GAKI: Oh, my God,
this is turning into
a meet and greet for newbs.
CHROME: Hi there.
Nice to meet you.
Looks like this is where
the party is.
I got an invite, too.
Just like everyone else.
SHARO: Hi, welcome to the board
where everyone comes
to say hello.
BAKYURA: Hello, everyone.
Wait, what's up
with all the hellos?
SAKI: Hi, there.
[both chuckle]
‐ Oh.
[gasps]
[man singing in Japanese]
♪ ♪
WOMAN: Let's talk
about this girl again.
She's a top idol,
she's glamorous,
and she hides under the mask
of a demonic killer.
It's a twisted, gloomy tale
involving [indistinct].
Next time,
"Roses Have Thorns."