["Headhunt" by Okamoto's]
[man singing in Japanese]
♪ ♪
SHINRA: By the way,
Egor is the patient's name,
right?
‐ We were in
the same organization
back home in Russia.
‐ If only Masaomi were here.
ANRI: I wonder how he's doing.
IZAYA: Your vacation's over,
you piece of shit.
‐ Toramaru from Saitama, right?
Your gang's boss
is a ladies' man.
‐ Why don't you
shut the hell up,
you dreadlocked piece of‐‐
♪ ♪
‐ Let's play a game.
And don't worry.
It's just a simple wager.
The subject of the wager
will be the human soul.
For example, let's say
I ask you this question.
Can all human souls be bought
with money or not?
The key word here is "all."
The answer is, there are times
when you can buy them
and times when you can't.
Wouldn't you agree?
Humans will sometimes maintain
their morality,
even if they're offered
a billion dollars.
Other times,
they'll murder someone
over 1 yen.
So look at it this way.
The human soul is random,
and we bet on random things.
This offends some people.
They might say
that the human soul
isn't nearly as random
as a toss of a coin.
They might even get angry.
For instance,
let's say we created a bet
based on the question,
"Will one person
murder another?"
For those who answer,
"That person would never do
something like that,"
the coin has landed on heads
before the results are in.
So the odds were greater
that the person wouldn't kill.
Let's put aside what TV says
is publicly acceptable.
This is hypothetical, after all.
You see,
it's impossible to predict
what kind of person someone is
until they're put to the test,
and working
as an information broker,
I've done just that
to numerous people,
but it's not as if I have 100%
control over the human soul.
All I can do
is give them a push.
Let's say
that someone's crossing
an extremely perilous boundary.
I can affect
in which direction they step,
but I can't guarantee
they'll survive the crossing.
With that in mind,
let the game begin‐‐
NAMIE: How meaningless.
Meaningless.
Meaningless and laughable.
Too many humans exist
in this world.
All I need is Seiji.
Because nothing else matters
in this world
other than
my darling little brother.
‐ Come on. See if you can get
that one over there next.
The fluffy little one
in the middle.
‐ No fair!
You've already got one.
What about‐‐
NAMIE: Even my love for Seiji
is nothing.
It's meaningless
compared to Seiji himself.
And yet,
humans go on multiplying.
In this world. In this city.
It's irritating.
Truly irritating.
Meaningless.
So meaningless.
MAN: Move, damn it!
I said move it!
‐ Somebody stop him
before he gets away!
MAN: Hey! Watch out!
MAN: Come on!
MAN: Hey! Come back here!
MAN: [speaking Russian]
WOMAN: [speaking Russian]
MAIRU:
What happened, Kururi? Darn!
I was reading a porn magazine,
and I missed it.
KURURI: Quiet.
‐ Ah!
[man growls]
‐ Get out of the way!
CHIKAGE: You knocked over
three women just now,
didn't you?
I counted three.
WOMAN: Thank you so much.
‐ Hmm?
‐ He was shoplifting
from the store where I work.
‐ Please, there's really no need
to thank me,
since I only did what any
ordinary person would have done.
Oh, my gosh.
How did that happen?
‐ What? Oh, this.
He knocked me over
as he ran away.
[man grunting]
‐ Ah! Ah!
‐ Oh, pipe down, you degenerate.
For all I know,
you've got a wife or a daughter
or maybe a mom waiting
for you to come crawling home,
so I'll pass on killing you,
'cause I don't want to make
those ladies cry
for an asshole like you.
But you'd better remember
that a real man
doesn't raise his hand
against a lady.
You got that?!
Don't worry, folks.
Everything's okay.
I've settled the score
on your behalf.
Revenge doesn't really suit
a beautiful young lady
such as yourself.
Scumbag.
Oh, I'm sorry.
To tell the truth,
I'm fine
with doing the dirty work.
Oh.
GIRL: Rocchi!
‐ Any ideas?
I think I scared her.
‐ Forget that.
Check it out.
[police whistles trilling]
Come on, Rocchi.
GIRL: Hurry up!
CHIKAGE: Hey, hold on!
WOMAN: What are you doing?
CHIKAGE: I'm sorry, lovely lady.
I'd like to stay,
but I'm afraid
I have to be off now.
‐ [sighs]
Here already?
SHIZUO:
I got you some coffee, Tom.
What's wrong?
‐ Oh, nothing.
I saw a familiar face walk by
just now.
Which reminds me,
he might have come by
to settle some business
with you.
‐ Huh?
‐ You remember.
You got in a fight
with some bikers from Saitama
not too long ago.
Pretty much destroyed 'em.
That gang is called
the Toramaru,
and their boss just walked by.
Guy's name is Chikage Rokujo,
by the way.
‐ You wouldn't be talking about
a guy in a white leather jacket
with a pink heart on the back,
would you?
‐ Huh? So you know the guy?
‐ Yeah. He showed up last night.
‐ Shizuo Heiwajima.
I've been looking for you.
‐ Huh?
CHIKAGE: Seems you took care
of some of my boys.
Considering the fact
they started raising hell
around here without my say‐so,
they kind of brought it
on themselves.
But you put 'em in the hospital.
Now, I'm not here to argue
about who was in the wrong,
since it was totally us,
but I do have an issue with you
overreacting to the situation.
NAMIE: Revenge for his men?
How meaningless.
There's nothing worth taking
revenge for in this world.
Other than my darling Seiji,
that is.
‐ Hey. Is there a woman
who really cares for you?
SHIZUO: Huh?
CHIKAGE: If so,
I don't want to make her cry,
so I'd be okay with looking
the other way this one time.
You see, making women cry
really isn't my thing.
SHIZUO: Oh, I get it.
So you're picking a fight
with me, is that it?
‐ Suppose I am.
‐ Just checking.
Nobody's been this up‐front
with me since high school.
At any rate,
I kind of like the fact
that you're coming right out
with it,
not going behind my back.
Although I'd prefer
not to do this at all.
‐ Sorry to disappoint.
‐ Oh, and before we start,
let me say one thing‐‐
‐ Heh.
‐ I was gonna say.
As my name suggests,
I like to live a quiet life.
So how should I put this?
It's nap time.
MIKADO: "Evening.
"Huh? Nobody's here?
"Guess I'll hang out.
"Oh, my partner's calling me,
so I'll be AFK."
‐ "Good evening, everyone.
"Oh, is it just you, Setton?
"Huh? No reply.
"It looks like
you're still busy.
"Pardon me.
I'll just hang out."
KYO: I apologize for getting
in the middle of this
while everyone's
apparently away.
Taro said that they were both
online and waited around,
while Setton,
unaware that someone is waiting,
is still unaccounted for.
This is the spark of romance,
isn't it?
Oh, but their genders aren't
something I know for sure.
Could it be possible
that there's a woman
behind the handle "Taro"?
And what about Setton?
We don't know if...
SAN: Huh?
KYO: Sorry. Character limit.
I can't tell what gender
Setton is by handle alone,
and it's such an unusual name
in the first place.
Where does it come from?
I just did an Internet search,
and all I came up with
was Korean costumes.
Or perhaps it was borrowed
from Maxwell Setton,
the filmmaker.
‐ It's a mystery.
SETTON: I'm back.
Good evening.
We've got an intense crowd here.
It's actually a play
on my real name.
KYO: I see.
So it was that simple?
I should've guessed.
Hmm. What kind of wordplay
is it, anyway?
[speaking in Japanese]
SAN: [speaking in Japanese]
SETTON: [speaking in Japanese]
[duck quacks]
SAN: What?
SETTON: This is the first time
I've ever seen that function.
Wait, what did you think
it was short for?
[duck quacks]
SAN: Ouch.
SETTON: Hmm?
SAN: I got pinched.
Ugh!
KURURI: Mm‐mm.
♪ ♪
ANRI: "Yo."
"Hey, the Preacher of Puns
has made his entrance."
"Lame‐dy‐killer."
"Hey, what do you mean, 'lame'?"
"Evening."
Good evening.
‐ [sighs]
"Hey. Ten seconds after me."
"You're in sync."
TARO: Whoa.
Suddenly so crowded here.
‐ "Oh. Taro's back now too."
"It's synchronicity, isn't it?"
"Sin‐chronic‐city.
"Kind of sounds like
it should be the last stage
in some video game, doesn't it?"
TARO: Does that honestly matter?
‐ "By the way,
is anybody planning
on going anywhere
over the long weekend?"
"I'll most likely be playing
video games with my partner."
[gasps]
♪ ♪
It's Masaomi!
It was him!
I knew it!
This is Masaomi, right?
MASAOMI: Heh.
That shouldn't matter right now.
MIKADO: Sorry. I only said
"does it honestly matter"
at the spur of the moment.
[sighs] I suspected it was you
and everything,
but I never thought
we'd able to talk
knowing it was really you!
I hope you're not really mad,
though.
I actually thought
"sin‐chronic‐city"
was kind of funny.
MASAOMI:
I wasn't talking about that.
MIKADO:
I see you've kicked the habit
of hitting enter
every time you use a comma.
MASAOMI: More or less.
Are you
going out anywhere this weekend?
MIKADO:
Well, I've got committee work
at school on Saturday.
But nothing else,
so we could meet up.
Anri really wants
to see you too.
MASAOMI: No.
That's not what this is about.
♪ ♪
‐ "Mikado,
you shouldn't wander around
"during the long weekend,
especially at night.
And stay away from the Dollars
for a while."
Huh? What's up?
MASAOMI:
I don't have all the details,
so I don't know
what to tell you.
But something's brewing.
The Dollars are in danger.
At least, I've got the feeling
that they are.
MIKADO: The Dollars?
I don't really get it, but okay.
After all, your gut feelings
are always right.
MASAOMI: Thanks, Mikado.
Watch your back.
NAMIE: A warning
from a deeply missed friend.
Best friends. Camaraderie.
How meaningless.
‐ Playing with your cell phone
again?
‐ No.
Just checking my signal.
Coverage has been pretty spotty
ever since we got here.
It's no big deal.
‐ You're up to something.
‐ Huh?
What do you mean?
SHINRA: Sorry to interrupt
all your fun, Celty.
We've got company.
TOM: Whoa. Did hell freeze over?
It's not like you to take
someone to the doctor, Shizuo.
‐ I can't really say
that I hate guys like him.
If it was the Fleabag,
I'd finish him off for sure.
‐ The Fleabag?
Oh, the information broker.
Well, if that guy took
one of your punches,
then that's basically the same
thing as getting finished off.
SHIZUO: Four punches.
‐ Uh?
‐ It took four,
and even after that,
he still got back on his feet.
Amazing.
‐ Are you serious?
‐ Yeah. And before
I hit him a fifth time,
he said,
"Unlike you, I've got a girl
"who's gonna nurse me
back to health.
Aren't you jealous?"
Or something like that.
He pretty much fell over
as soon as he got that out.
‐ I knew
he was a tough son of a bitch,
but even so.
‐ To tell the truth,
it did make me kind of jealous.
‐ Hey, don't worry.
You'll find a cute girl
one of these days.
After all, you look like
your hot idol of a kid brother.
‐ Do we really look
that much alike?
‐ Okay. We grabbed a snack
here at Lottaria,
so for dinner, how about
we balance it out with what‐‐
huh?
‐ What's the matter?
‐ You tell me.
‐ Huh?
‐ [sighs]
Hmm? Uh...
[laughing]
‐ That girl
a relative of yours, Shizuo?
‐ No.
I've never seen her before.
‐ I don't get the feeling
she's staring at you
because of the way
you're dressed or anything.
‐ Doesn't seem like it.
I'll go see what's up.
‐ Hey, hold on a sec.
What you gonna do
if she starts calling you
"daddy" or "darling"?
‐ Yeah, that's not gonna happen.
♪ ♪
NAMIE: She looked innocent,
much like a doll.
Like purity itself.
This idiot man doesn't know
there are many different kinds
of innocence.
‐ It's time to die.
NAMIE:
Like an innocence that allows
someone to kill a stranger,
just like that,
in the name of love,
like this one.
[electricity crackles]
CHIKAGE: Hey, thanks for showing
me around Ikebukuro today.
GIRL: [giggles]
Sure thing!
GIRL: Oh, by the way, Rocchi,
are you feeling any better?
GIRL: We weren't expecting you
to be all beat to a pulp
when you showed up today.
GIRL: Yeah, really.
You suck at fights.
You shouldn't bite off
more than you can chew.
CHIKAGE: I don't suck.
GIRL: So you're saying you won?
CHIKAGE: Not quite.
‐ Figured you'd say that.
‐ Yeah,
but the guy I was fighting
was way too strong,
and it's been a while
since I was in a real fight‐‐
NAMIE: How meaningless.
Thinking that women are things
that must be protected.
That they're not to be hurt.
There's no need for us to be
protected by the likes of you.
GIRL:
In any case, it's crazy to ask
eight girls out on a date
at the same time.
GIRL: I think it was actually
more like ten‐‐
NAMIE: We're not so frail
that someone like you
could hurt us.
GIRL: Why are we hanging out
with a womanizer like him
anyway?
NAMIE:
Remember, we women are strong.
Especially
women who fall in love.
‐ I'm sorry for making you come
all the way out here
to discuss this job.
Oh, can I get you
a hot towel or something?
‐ Please,
don't go to any trouble.
Um, for some reason,
I feel like everyone's on edge.
‐ Huh? Oh, no.
Not at all.
There was an incident
at the office
of one of our associates.
Apparently,
someone dressed like you
showed up there the other day
and submitted
what you might consider
a violent claim.
‐ Would you like me to change?
[to self] Not being able
to show irritation
at times like these
is a plus for me.
HARUYA: There's no reason
for you to feel irritated.
‐ [to self] Is he psychic?
Can you read people's minds?
‐ In my business,
if you want to stay alive,
you learn to read body language.
We'd like you to relax,
so if you want
to take your helmet off,
please go ahead.
‐ Are you absolutely sure?
‐ Of course.
In fact,
I believe it's normal for people
to take their helmets off
when they're indoors.
♪ ♪
‐ Sh‐she's a freak!
‐ What the hell
were you thinking
saying something like that
about one of our guests?
Didn't you hear
what I just said to her?
I said it's normal for people
to remove their helmets indoors!
‐ I'm sorry!
‐ You're apologizing
to the wrong person.
I'm not the one you insulted!
‐ I really don't mind.
‐ You're very forgiving.
Honestly,
I'm sorry you were exposed
to such an ugly sight.
‐ Don't worry about it.
[to self]
These people are really twisted.
‐ Perhaps it would be best
if we got back to business.
‐ Huh?
‐ Ah!
That hurt.
MAN: Did you see that?
SHIZUO: What is this?
Using a stun gun?
‐ I got a bad feeling.
‐ Hmm.
MAN: He knocked that girl down.
‐ Not good.
No matter which way
you look at it.
‐ Uh, we got trouble coming,
Shizuo.
[police whistles trilling]
Let's get out of here.
We're not gonna be able
to talk our way out of this!
‐ You won't... get away!
Quit running... and die!
‐ Got any ideas
on what to do with this kid?
‐ Huh? Whoa! That little brat's
a pain in the ass.
You got a friend's house
we can head to?
This is way too conspicuous.
SHIZUO: What about the office?
TOM: We can't get
the company involved.
Hey! What about
your kid brother's apartment?
‐ No good. It's always crawling
with paparazzi.
TOM: [groans]
‐ Damn it!
Can't you think of anyplace?
What about that pervert?
The doctor we talked about?
He's always into
weird stuff like this,
so he shouldn't mind.
‐ Got it.
Let's go!
AKANE: Die. Die!
MAN: Can't believe you lost
in a one‐on‐one fight.
‐ Yeah. That one wasn't human.
To be honest, I never want
to fight that him again.
MAN: I can't believe
he's that much of a badass.
‐ Well, I'm the one
who picked the fight,
so there's no reason
to take him on again.
MAN: Yeah. I hear that.
‐ [laughs]
Yep.
Shizuo Heiwajima
was just a detour.
We'll be taking on
our real enemies
starting tonight.
An eye for an eye.
A tooth for a tooth.
Honor for honor.
Those guys
want to play dirty with us?
Then we'll show them
what playing dirty is all about.
‐ Three more of our guys
got jumped yesterday.
‐ Shit. And they think they can
do whatever the hell they want.
We're not exactly
sweet and innocent, you know,
so there's really no need
to fight fair and square
against a shitload of fools
like them.
I don't know
if you can call this payback,
but they came
all the way to Saitama
and ambushed not only our guys
but even people who have got
nothing at all to do with us.
‐ Ugh. I don't know what kind
of street cred they have here,
but I hear
these guys in the Dollars‐‐
they're seriously insane.
‐ I don't give a rat's ass
about this gang!
Or their stupid freaking name!
'Cause
when we're done with them,
all they're gonna know is
they messed with the wrong guys.
So let's head on in there
and show
those bastards in the Dollars
which one of us
is really insane!
ALL: Yeah!
[loud cheering]
NAMIE: Yes.
Go on
destroying each other like that.
BOTH: Huh?
NAMIE: Go on and die.
‐ All right,
and before I forget,
I'm sure you guys
from the main gang know this,
but if anyone raises a hand
against a lady,
even if she's in the Dollars,
I'm gonna track your ass down
and beat you to death myself.
‐ Oh, man.
What a pain.
Why did I even take this job?
[Cóiste‐Bodhar neighs]
Uh‐huh.
Thanks, Shooter.
[engine revving]
NAMIE: And yet,
humans go on multiplying.
In this world.
In this city.
It's irritating.
Truly irritating.
‐ Good evening,
my brave knight of Halloween.
Play time for children is over.
It's a shame.
NAMIE: How truly meaningless.
♪ ♪
[man singing in Japanese]
CELTY: Ikebukuro is heading
towards chaos again.
A mysterious young girl?
Russians? Biker gangs?
Yakuza? A sleazy talent agent?
What's going on?
And most importantly,
what will happen to me?
Next time‐‐
"A Crow in the Dark Night."