["Day You Laugh"
by Toyonaga Toshiyuki]
♪ ♪
[man singing in Japanese]
‐ You're gonna give us
your phones,
and we're gonna cancel your
membership with the Dollars.
‐ Her stalker
is in the Dollars?
‐ The security cameras
caught a sketchy‐looking guy
in the hallway
outside her door.
‐ I'm going back
to Ikebukuro tomorrow.
‐ My whole life,
all the way up until now,
I felt like I had
to destroy everything.
[man singing in Japanese]
♪ ♪
[Japanese pop music plays]
MAN: Hello?
Hello?
‐ [singing in Japanese]
♪ ♪
WOMAN: She had a dream once,
to have the power to shape
her own destiny.
It was inspired by
the grandmother she never knew,
but that was her secret.
Ruri Hijiribe was born
and raised in a little town
tucked deep
in the Kanto Mountains.
After her father
and grandfather went bankrupt,
the family home burned
to the ground mysteriously.
Then her mother disappeared,
and shortly after, her father.
Her mother was a Hijiribe,
and her father and grandfather
had married into the family.
Ruri had never seen
her grandmother, not once.
She didn't know if it was
due to divorce or death.
When she asked about her,
she got vague answers.
She couldn't find a picture
of her anywhere.
But her grandfather always said
he loved her grandmother.
‐ You look just like
your grandma.
WOMAN: He told her she
was kind and always smiled.
But the people in town
had an entirely different
opinion of her.
‐ Hey, you.
You're the girl who's got
a monster for a grandma.
‐ That means you're one, too!
all: Monster!
Monster! Monster!
[laughter]
WOMAN: Hearing this...
‐ [chuckles]
WOMAN: ...made her happy.
She didn't know why,
but the notion made her
feel warm inside, comforted.
Soon, she became infatuated
with the monsters
she saw on television
and at the movies.
They represented freedom
and destruction.
And since she lived
in an oppressive home,
she wanted more than anything
to know what they felt like.
After the fire,
Ruri left home to find work.
She apprenticed with
Tenjin Zakuroya,
a master of special effects
makeup.
She thought if she could
bring her dreams to life,
maybe she could get closer
to her grandmother.
Her success led to
an encounter with a man.
‐ Huh?
‐ Pleased to meet you,
my dear.
The name's Yodogiri.
I must say, those monsters
of yours are quite remarkable.
With your looks, you'd be
a different kind of monster,
a pop idol monster.
You'd rule the world.
Hello?
Is anyone there?
‐ Oh, it's you.
YODOGIRI: Oh, Mr. Adabashi,
you take so long to answer,
I never know if I called
the right number.
Why do you do that?
‐ Enjoying the moment.
YODOGIRI: Pardon?
‐ The moment I get to decide
when to kill Ruri's voice
with one push.
YODOGIRI: Ah.
‐ I get to smash her with
the press of my thumb.
I get to end her
just like that.
And I get off every second
up till when I do.
YODOGIRI: Oh‐oh‐oh,
naturally, naturally.
And who can blame you?
After all, she is
the one who killed your father.
‐ Who cares about
that piece of shit?
My dad's better off dead,
anyway.
I'm kind of jealous
she got to kill him.
YODOGIRI: Yes, of course.
Of course you are.
Understandable.
‐ All right, Mr. Yodogiri,
why you calling?
YODOGIRI: Well,
remember how in exchange
for information
on Miss Hijiribe,
you agreed to do me a favor
at some point in time?
I was hoping to‐‐
oh, what's the phrase?‐‐
cash it in?
‐ What do you want?
YODOGIRI: It appears Ruri has
recently made the acquaintance
of the Headless Rider.
‐ Okay, so what about it?
[meows]
‐ Um, sorry,
lost my train of thought.
‐ Something about
the Dollars, remember?
‐ Oh, right.
I wasn't really
in too deep with those guys,
but Celty here was.
She can tell you
more about them than I can.
‐ Yeah, that's great and all,
but you can't just
show up out of the blue
with Kasuka and Ruri Hijiribe.
I mean, come on, you could
have at least sent a text first.
‐ I'm sorry.
We don't want to bother you.
‐ Oh, my God, no.
You're not bothering anyone.
Why, Celty and I are both
super huge fans of you guys.
I mean, if I knew
you were coming,
I would have picked up
some turkey and a cheesecake
at the store.
‐ But you've done
so much already.
You took care of me
the other day,
and I'll always
be grateful for that.
‐ Wait, you mean,
you guys have met before?
‐ Um...
‐ Oh, yeah.
A couple of days ago
she was in rough shape.
Kasuka found her
and brought her over here,
and yours truly got her
all fixed up, good as new.
‐ Hmm.
RURI: I can't believe
the Headless Rider
is here with the doc.
Oh, no, I wonder if she
recognized me.
CELTY:
Oh, I never met her before,
but I'm getting
this familiar vibe.
ANRI: What's going on?
Saika's all confused.
Is she human or a monster?
Do we love her or hate her?
[meow]
[gasps]
[meowing]
[gasping]
‐ Oh, can one of you guys
watch the cat?
GAKI: So a friend of mine
invited me to this chat.
I'm here, but what does
everyone normally talk about?
SHARO: According to the log,
the stalker.
Is anyone on here
a member of the Dollar?
CHROME: I'm a Dollar.
At least I'm registered as one.
GAKI: Same here.
I only registered.
SHARO: If I signed up,
would I be cool?
If so, I'm in.
‐ Ooh, Scottish Folds
are her favorite.
Duly noted.
Oh, no way, they're
reprinting her photo book.
Better jump on that pre‐order.
‐ Oh, man,
does he buy that thing
every time they put it out
or what?
‐ He's a hardcore fanboy.
Bow down, bow down.
‐ That son of a bitch
is still around.
‐ Hmm?
Who are you talking about?
‐ It's just some asshat
in Ruri's forums.
He keeps posting this shit
about having all these
secret pics of her.
Scumbag.
Freakin' dweeb's handle
is Living Sacrifice Boy.
‐ Oh, come on,
don't give us that.
I know you really want
to see them,
especially if they're shots
of Ruri naked.
‐ Hey, show some respect,
will you?
It's Miss Hijiribe to you,
you non‐fan philistine.
‐ Whoa, take a chill pill,
buddy.
‐ You hear the rumor
going around
how Miss Ruri's stalker
might be in the Dollars?
‐ Yeah, and if I find out
who he is,
I'm gonna drive this thing
straight up his ass
while he's sleeping.
‐ Before you do,
you mind letting us out?
Getting stuck in someone's ass
isn't on my bucket list.
MAN: Thank you very much.
‐ Hmm?
Hey, Mikado.
You're out kind of late tonight.
‐ Yeah, I'm on my way home
from a friend's.
So how's everything
been going with you?
Wait, don't tell me you're
heading off to work now.
‐ Yeah, night shift.
Just had dinner,
so it's back to the grind.
KYO: Hey, I think I figured out
who Sharo is IRL.
SAN: No way, really?
KYO: I bet you're
Sharon Stone.
Am I right or am I right?
SAN: Ehh!
‐ So how's Masaomi doing?
You talk to him much?
‐ Not in person.
Only by email and stuff.
‐ Cool.
As long as he's doing okay.
How you doing?
Are you still rolling
with the Dollars, or what?
‐ Me?
Are you kidding?
Of course I am.
‐ Figured.
Then I guess you know
about these people
going around
calling themselves Dollars
and being dicks.
‐ Uh‐huh, but as far
as I'm concerned,
anyone who acts like that
isn't a real Dollar.
‐ Yeah, well, isn't it
the point of being a Dollar
that you're free
to do whatever?
‐ Sure, if they're like you.
You're a role model for us.
‐ Say what?
‐ Things would be a lot more
peaceful around here
if the Dollars had more people
like you and Celty in it.
Think about it,
there wouldn't be anyone
using the Dollars' name
to do crimes or hurt people.
Everyone in town would know
if they were in a jam,
the Dollars would have
their back.
‐ You sound like you know
what's best for everyone.
‐ Maybe I do, maybe I don't.
But like you said, as a Dollar,
I'm free to do whatever,
even if it means trying
to make things better here.
‐ [sighs]
‐ Well, I guess
I'll see you later.
‐ Okay, see you around.
I hope he hasn't
gone off the rails.
If Izaya's screwing
with his head
like he did with Masaomi's...
[engine rumbling]
[tires squealing]
Dragon Zombie jacket.
They're back in town.
Great.
‐ Come back tomorrow, mister.
And next day,
and next day, next day.
But you go rest in peace
until, huh?
Hmm?
‐ [humming]
YODOGIRI: Great job tonight.
Do you have any plans?
We're having a party
for our sponsors.
In fact,
our biggest will be there,
the CEO of Adabashi
Life Insurance.
‐ [gasps]
‐ Your presence would be
appreciated.
By the way, my dear,
have you heard anything
from your family?
‐ Uh‐uh.
[gasps]
‐ Are you okay?
‐ Did I fall asleep?
I'm sorry.
How embarrassing.
‐ What do you expect?
You haven't had
a decent night's sleep
for the past few days.
‐ I hope you're exaggerating.
Superstars need sleep
just like everyone else.
[cat meows]
‐ No, Dokusonmaru.
Stop that.
‐ There goes my research.
I have to start over,
but I found the forum
Yuhei was talking about.
The Dollars have tons of
little communities in it now.
‐ The first thing we should do
is figure out how to
deal with the stalker.
‐ What about the cat?
‐ I don't know.
We don't keep
normal people hours,
so we can't take care of it.
[cat mewls]
[meow]
‐ If Yuhei and Dokusonmaru
get dragged into this...
WOMAN: "If anyone has to die,
let me be the one," she prayed.
"Just me and no one else."
After taking so many lives
as Hollywood the serial killer,
a prayer like this from her
was, in a word, hypocritical.
He knew everything about her,
how she must be feeling now.
He knew what really went on at
these parties with the sponsors
because his father was one.
Looking to blackmail him,
he followed his father
to one of these parties.
He peeked in, saw Ruri,
and fell madly in love with her.
[suspenseful music]
♪ ♪
‐ [chuckles]
WOMAN: He knew
what he had to do.
To really love her, he had
to shatter her heart first.
So he committed himself
to the task.
‐ [laughs]
‐ Okay, what'd you guys
call me over here for?
‐ Well, when it comes to
stalking, you're the master.
‐ What are you saying?
I'm not a stalker!
When have I ever stalked?
‐ Well, you used to stalk.
‐ There, you see, I used
to stalk, but not anymore.
‐ [chuckles]
‐ Okay then,
as a former stalker,
would it be easy to pick
the locks on a newer building,
like this one?
‐ Oh, Celty, you're so funny.
I wouldn't call any of the locks
around here hard to pick.
Would someone lock
the door behind me?
I'm gonna give
a demonstration.
I'll be back in a sec,
okay, Seiji?
I'm gonna work faster
knowing my man's
on the other side
of the door.
‐ One locked door coming up.
‐ Your friend is,
how should I put it, active?
‐ Yeah, she's amazing, huh?
MIKA: Let's see,
for this kind of lock
there's about a dozen ways
you can pick it.
You can use a thumb‐turn device
or a bump key.
With some practice,
anyone can do it,
even a little kid.
So you might want to think
about upgrading your locks.
E‐locks are pretty reliable.
all: What the‐‐
‐ Ta‐da!
Seiji!
‐ What are we gonna do, Celty?
Should we change the locks
or should we move or what?
You got any ideas?
‐ I don't know.
I'll go scope out Ruri
and Yuhei's apartment building.
Maybe I'll get a lead.
‐ [clapping]
Oh, my God!
I can't believe it, my two
superstars are super early.
Why can't all my clients
be more like you?
‐ Why can't you
be more like them?
You arrived here
20 minutes late.
‐ Time is relative.
Or something.
Besides, what's 20 minutes
out of the 13 billion years
of the history
of the universe?
Nothing, I tell you!
Nothing!
Then again, what's the saying,
time is money?
Sure, I'll give 'em that,
I guess.
But there's more to life
than money, kids.
Am I right?
I can think of two things,
babies.
Heart and soul.
I've gone off on
another tangent, haven't I?
‐ Yes, and you've wasted
25 minutes.
‐ Then let's get to it!
Now, Mr. Yuhei, would you
please go stand in that corner
and face the wall?
You can listen in
if you'd like.
‐ Of course.
‐ This arrived in the mail
yesterday.
I do not like having
to show it to the star
I'm sworn to protect,
but if it means
we can catch this creep
or kill him or whatever,
we need to make sure
it's legit.
‐ Huh?
[gasps, whimpers]
‐ I was afraid of this.
This thing didn't look fake
like the others we've gotten.
Sorry to put you
through this, hon,
but you have any idea
who might have sent it?
‐ I do, but first I‐‐
I'd like for Yuhei to take
a look at it.
WOMAN: Shall we start?
ADABASHI: I don't know.
WOMAN: Don't worry,
Mr. Adabashi.
There's no risk.
Once we begin, everyone here
will be an accomplice.
ADABASHI: [gasps]
Incredible.
The wound is closing up
all on its own.
Is she immortal or something?
WOMAN: It's possible,
but I'm not sure.
We haven't been able
to confirm it yet.
‐ Where did President Yodogiri
find this girl?
‐ He only just learned of the
Hijiribes' strange bloodline.
‐ He's a lucky man.
I always said so.
‐ He's not the only one.
Things are looking up
for us now as well.
WOMAN: Until that night,
she had no idea
the blood of a monster
coursed through her veins.
That night she discovered
the real reason
Yodogiri approached her,
the reason he was interested.
‐ Your father
came to see me today,
and he said
he wanted you back.
‐ [gasps]
‐ I asked him to leave
but he wouldn't,
so we took him someplace where
he wouldn't cause problems.
You know what that means,
yes?
It would be in your father's
best interests,
and mine as well,
for you to carry on
as my dutiful product.
[crowd cheering]
WOMAN:
It was easy to verify.
While searching online
for information
on her father's whereabouts,
a man told her what he knew,
free of charge.
Her father had been killed
by Yodogiri and his men.
She remembers screaming,
and so it was born,
deep in her heart,
the monster.
A demon called Hollywood,
terrifying, homicidal,
bent on revenge.
‐ Yuhei, when I tried to tell
you about my past before,
you told me it didn't matter,
that you didn't need
to know about it, but I have‐‐
‐ I don't think now is the best
time to tell me about it.
‐ [gasps]
‐ You should wait until
you're up to it.
Nothing I say can help you.
You'll have to make peace
with your past.
I can't do it for you.
‐ [gasps]
‐ Can I just say
you're the perfect couple!
Here's an idea,
let's put out a photo book
with you guys together!
Yeah, but first things first,
we gotta deal with this photo.
This Jinnai Yodogiri guy,
he sounds nastier
than the rumors say.
Only a dyed‐in‐the‐wool perv
would force an innocent flower
like yourself
into performing in some‐‐
some kinky porno.
‐ Huh?
‐ He talks a good game,
but I'm sure he knows
that picture isn't from a porn.
So don't worry about it, okay?
Even though Max
is a selfish, overambitious,
lawbreaking criminal,
I believe underneath it all
he's got your best
interests at heart.
‐ I'm back, but I need
to find out what's going on.
Maybe I should square things
with everyone first.
Uh.
Oh, crap.
I can't believe I'm doing this.
Nice knowing you, Saki,
Anri, Mikado.
‐ I feel bad for putting you
on the spot.
I'm sorry.
‐ No worries!
By the way, how's Mikado
doing these days?
You guys getting along okay?
You kiss him yet?
‐ What?
Oh, no, of course not.
‐ That's a bummer.
Anyhoo, if you need anything,
give me a shout.
I'm happy to lend a hand,
just try to time it
for when I'm not with Seiji.
‐ Uh, sorry.
When are you never
not with me?
‐ Thanks, Mika.
[cat meows]
MASAOMI: Sorry to bother you,
Mr. Heiwajima.
I've been meaning to tell you
I'm sorry for a while now,
for getting in your way.
‐ Do I know you?
‐ Not exactly.
We never met.
I'm Masaomi.
‐ Wait, where have I
heard that name?
[gunshot]
‐ Don't blame me!
Masaomi Kida ordered this hit!
‐ Oh.
That's right.
I remember now.
‐ Hey, easy, easy.
‐ Go ahead and hit me
if you want.
I deserve it.
‐ Maybe.
But I don't go around
beating up kids.
Celty told me about you
and how those dumb shits
were using your name
to get me to go after you.
‐ Who's Celty?
Never mind, it's all my fault.
I should have been paying
more attention back then.
If I did, then you wouldn't
have gotten shot‐‐
‐ Like I said,
I don't beat up kids.
‐ [groans]
‐ I don't have any grudge
against the Yellow Scarves
anymore,
but if you're looking
for closure or some shit,
that flick to the dome
makes us even.
Cool?
‐ No, man, can you, like,
dial it back just a little?
‐ You're kidding.
I just flicked him.
‐ I have question,
what martial art
teaches this ultimate
technique called flick?
‐ Same one that teaches
the smack.
You hear about that one?
‐ The smack?
‐ You okay?
‐ That depends.
‐ As long as you can talk,
I guess you're good.
If you're feeling up to it,
you wanna grab a bite
to eat with us?
‐ Uh, okay.
[doorbell chimes]
‐ [chuckles]
MAN: Package for you.
‐ Coming, coming.
[gasps]
[suspenseful music]
‐ Something tells me you're not
really a delivery man.
[groans]
Celty.
[groaning]
♪ ♪
[man singing in Japanese]
WOMAN: As the stalker
incident comes to a head,
everyone who's been dragged
into this nightmare
will be left scarred.
And when all is said and done,
the only thing left
is the sound of laughter.
Next time,
"A Cat has Nine Lives."