♪ [theme song playing]
♪ [man singing in Japanese]
[grunting]
[Erika] What do you have,
that'll save the heroine
of this story?
[Anri]
What have you done with them?
Nothing yet,
but they'll be here soon.
She might have
her old memories back,
and she might even kill me.
What is it
you wanted to show me?
The last meeting
of the Dollars.
♪ [singing resumes]
♪ [ends]
[Masaomi]
Sure, I wanted
to see him again.
I dreamed about
the day I could.
If that sounds creepy to you,
then stop watching.
'Cause, from now on,
things are gonna get creepy.
[panting]
People I know...
[growls]
Their lives are
all connected.
The ties that bind 'em
are gonna get so tangled up
and so messed up,
it's gonna make you sick.
The last meeting
of the Dollars.
[gasps]
[neighs]
[phone ringing]
Answer it.
Yes? Hello?
[Erika]
Ms. Kujiragi!
Thank God! You're okay!
I don't know if you're out
tonight, but if you are,
stay away
from the east side
of Ikebukuro!
I just barely got
away from 'em myself.
I'm sorry.
Got away from whom?
The Slasher, that's who!
Or, like, dozens of slashers.
Hundreds of 'em!
You know, with the red eyes?
And this guy was there.
I guess he was their leader,
or something.
And he said your name.
He said he was gonna
kill you and bury you!
This man you mentioned,
can you give me
a description of him?
Well, he looked like he was
from a host club, I guess.
Oh! And remember
when I met you?
There was that girl
you and Anri were with?
She was there with him
and was saying,
"Yes, Mother," to him.
It was so weird.
I didn't know what to do,
so I got the heck
out of there quick!
[Kujiragi]
Takashi Nasujima.
I appreciate your concern
for me, Ms. Karisawa.
Leave there as soon as you can
and please be careful.
You try and be careful,
too, okay?
And if you get
in a jam, call me!
Thank you again
for your concern.
Hello! What are
you ladies doing here?
Hey. You're the guy that was
buggin' my brother at the gym.
And you're that boyish-girl!
The tough-as-nails sister
of Gas Mask Three!
Gas mask what?
Number one's the brains!
Two's the skill!
Gorgeous when standing,
sexy when sitting,
hot when walking--
that's Gas Mask Three!
At first glance,
he's Adonis,
but get closer and he's just
your average muscle--
You'd better tell me
what you're doing here,
or my boot's goin'
up your ass.
Easy. I have business
with Ms. Kujiragi.
Now then, about that wire
you used to trap Celty...
It seems to have changed
into a Japanese sword.
I'm a scientist,
and I was wondering
if I could have it to study.
I would gladly part with it,
just as long as you pay
the market price.
Yes, well, about that, uh...
Why don't we step outside
and talk it over?
Heck, let's all talk it over!
Your motivation
is unclear to me.
And I prefer to speak
to Shizuo, not you.
[laughs]
I hope you brought
your running shoes!
Just now,
I saw him chasing Izaya
like a bat out of hell!
[both gasp]
[chuckles]
I guess you're the real
boss of these dipshits,
huh, champ?
But you look
like a smart kid.
You see anything wrong
with this crowd?
This guy's more
than we can handle!
What are we gonna do, man?
Stop freaking out
and wake Houjou up.
The more you ignore me,
the more pissed off I get.
Sorry about that.
I'm still trying to process
what you just did.
Yeah, well, I was
holdin' back a bit.
Is everyone
from the Saitama gang
as strong as you?
[people clamoring]
Kinda funny those guys
picked tonight for a meet-up,
don't ya think?
As of tonight, they're
not a biker gang anymore.
I'd like you to meet
the new members of the Dollars.
[phones beeping]
And I bet you just
emailed 'em about me, huh?
You know it! Don't you
just love technology?
I told 'em you're
an enemy of the Dollars.
What's with
that God-awful racket?
Oh, well. They'll all be part
of my Saika army soon enough.
Oh, yeah? Jeez.
How many are we talkin' here?
So far, 13 have showed up.
That's pretty much
every major biker-gang
in the Kanto area, sir.
All right.
Well, you guys keep
a low profile out there.
Make sure you don't get
into it with any of those
red-eyed people either.
[sighs]
You're having way too much fun
tonight, Mikado. Way too much.
What the hell's
goin' on down there?
A shit-load of biker gangs
just showed up!
There's more
than bikers down there.
There's also
plain old thugs, too.
From Chiba and Saitama.
They all got called in.
What? You got a bunch
of goons to come here?
What are you, friggin' crazy?
Dude, what are you doin',
messin' around with
those kinds of people?
I made people like that
leave the Dollars once before.
Then, I realized
that wasn't enough.
I had to hit 'em
where it hurts.
It's kinda funny.
These guys will beat up
someone, no problem.
But, if you threaten
to leak nasty details about
their families, they panic.
Hold on.
Are you sayin' you--?
Mikado, where'd you get that?
Too much has happened.
What the hell
are you doin' with that?
Have you totally
lost your mind, man?
You bring the Dollars
out here, and for what?
If I wasn't such an asshole--
I'm supposed to be your friend,
and I don't even know what
you're doing or why anymore!
No. It's not your fault.
It's my fault things
turned out like this.
So, tonight,
the Dollars are done.
What?
You're shutting it down?
I guess I am, in a way.
At least, that's what's
going to happen.
Look at all the people
down in the street.
Every one of them
is a Dollar.
I wanted you and Anri
to see the scope of this
amazing thing I made.
[gasps]
You wanted... this?
It gave me
kind of a thrill at first.
But, then,
I got bored with it.
And that got me thinking...
"What if I could
turn it into something
you and Anri could
be a part of?"
I was so proud
of this thing I made,
and I wanted
to share it with you.
What's the point
if it ain't gonna
be around anymore?
After the Dollars'
first meeting,
Izaya gave me a warning.
He said, even if I escaped
my boring life,
it'll all seem ordinary
soon enough.
He was right.
The Dollars were ordinary
before I knew it.
Sure enough, I was bored.
He was playing you,
you idiot!
That son of a bitch
tells you one thing,
then tells someone else
the opposite!
Then, he sits back and laughs
at how everyone
around him suffers!
I know that's his deal,
but still, even if
he didn't say anything,
I would've gotten bored.
That's just another trick!
He makes you think
that you're the one who--
Hey, what do you think
you're doing?
I guess even a guy like you
is afraid of getting shot.
It's my fault.
No. I ended up like this
because I chose to.
You had nothing
to do with it.
Then why are you
pointing that at me?
I don't know.
I guess I haven't thought
this whole thing through yet.
Then what the hell
do you have it for?
You got no business
carryin' that thing around!
Throw that thing
in the goddamn river
before you use it!
But I already have.
[gasps]
Dotachin!
You're all right! Dotachin!
[grunts]
Yumatchi, let go of me!
Take it easy, Erika!
We're gonna perform
an exorcism on you!
Huh?
I'm sorry about this, Erika.
It won't hurt at all.
Just a little cut
on your fingertip.
[screams]
What are you talking about?
Don't deny it!
You're totally infected!
Your red eyeballs
are a dead giveaway!
No, they're contacts!
Contacts!
I'm wearing
my red cosplay contacts!
Huh?
Contacts?
Can't you tell
by how she's acting?
Let her go already.
[moaning]
I swear, you guys...
Way to spoil
the tearful reunion scene!
Sorry we scared you.
Yeah, sorries!
Dude!
... are still coming in,
but here's what
we know so far.
There were two shootings
earlier today.
The first happened outside
Ikebukuro Police Station.
The second happened
at the entrance to the home
of Doh-gen Awakusu,
the head of the powerful crime
syndicate, the Awakusu Group.
What appears to be graffiti,
spray-painted on the wall
next to the entryway,
looks to be the work
of a local group
of troublemakers.
Police are still
trying to determine
if the two shootings
are related.
Oh, great.
Take a guess who
the local troublemakers are.
Dollars. They just stepped
in some deep shit.
[Aozaki]
Goddamn it.
I didn't think
he was so off his nut,
he'd pull
somethin' like this.
If he's takin' shots
at his place,
it's the same as takin' 'em
at the Awakusu's.
It's my fault
that little shit did this,
and now, I get to lose
a couple of fingers over it.
Get Mikado and take him
somewheres quiet.
Right.
Sir! Mr. Akabayashi
just showed up
and says he wants
to talk to you, alone.
Just what I needed.
This is how
the Dollars ends.
Once the word gets out
about the shootings
at the police station
and at the Awakusu boss' house,
everyone who's
in the Dollars now, will quit.
No members, no Dollars.
And then, it'll become
an urban legend.
People are gonna talk about 'em
for years and years and years.
And, as the rumors about 'em
pile up, it'll evolve.
And, in the end, the Dollars
will finally become perfect.
That's the dumbest thing
I ever heard.
Shooting up a Yakuza's house
and a police station for that?
Are you gonna stop me?
What do you want to do?
I never did a single
good thing for you, did I?
Well, right now,
all I want to do is beat
the living hell out of you!
Masaomi...
I'm gonna knock your ass
back to that dumb,
boring, ordinary life
you hate so much!
You're not some legend
like the Headless Rider,
that's for sure!
You're Mikado Ryugamine!
A stupid, skinny,
plain-old kid!
The same decent, ordinary kid
I used to know!
Nothing ever
gets you down, does it?
I wish I could be like that.
I always wanted
to be as strong as you.
No matter how
this ends tonight,
no matter if I get
called a coward,
I'm gonna prove
I'm anything but ordinary!
[grunts]
Jesus! I'm gonna kick
your ass for that! [gasps]
[indistinct chatter]
[groaning]
Dude, did you hear
what I just heard?
What?
Like a bang.
Who are you?
It's a bigger crowd
than I expected.
I see half
are Saika zombies.
This is great!
I can work with this.
What are you doin' here?
[chuckles]
[Chikage]
Holy shit. It's Heiwajima.
Don't tell me you called him
to back you up, too.
No, man. He's not
in the Dollars anymore.
Huh?
Alrighty,
time to start the show.
Did anyone else hear
a popping noise just now?
Uh-huh, I think
someone fired a gun.
Are you sure? All I can hear
is these goddamn bikers.
[Kujiragi]
You amaze me.
Huh?
I didn't think you would
overcome Saika's influence
so quickly.
Oh, you're Kasane
Ku-- Kujiragi!
You're, uh, not gonna
kidnap me again, are you?
Not at all. It would
be a waste of time
for both of us.
It's obvious your will
is too strong for Saika
to have control over.
Thank God!
I hope that doesn't mean
you're gonna kill me instead.
Actually,
I'm here to apologize.
Originally, I thought
you were pretending
to be in love with Celty.
I assumed your father
wanted you to keep her
under observation.
But, upon investigating
your situation further,
I became convinced
that your feelings
toward her were genuine.
As for myself,
I have never experienced
being loved by anyone.
And that gave me an idea.
Instead of waiting for love,
I would seek it out for myself.
That's why you kissed me!
If you could love
a creature like her,
you could love me.
Therefore, I could love you.
I was also jealous.
[gasps]
Forgive me
for being blunt,
but do you think
you could love me
as I love you?
Sorry, but I'm afraid
I can't return the sentiment.
I should be angry,
I mean, after everything
you put me through.
But I'm not
and you know why?
It's because I have Celty.
See, with her, I don't need
anything else in my life.
She's the reason
I can talk to you like this,
the reason I'm happy.
I'm who I am
because of her.
That's why
you feel about me
the way you do.
Very well.
Hearing you
say it so clearly,
I have to accept it.
[grunting]
The kind of love
she and I have,
anyone can have.
Would you like me
to prove it?
A guy like me
and a Headless Rider...
She and I couldn't
be any more different,
but even so, the two of us
fell in love, somehow.
You will too, I promise.
Until then, it doesn't matter
if it's family, or yourself.
The important thing
is to love someone.
What a horrible
person you are.
First you reject me,
then you make me
love you more.
[chuckles]
By the way, Ms. Kujiragi,
could you do me a little favor?
I don't know.
I could've sworn it came
from the building on the left.
I'm not 100% sure, though.
[gasps]
[all scream]
That dick!
Chill out, Saburo!
[laughing]
It's my lucky day today!
The league
of extraordinary assholes!
[laughing]
Izumii?
Huh? Izumii?
You dye your hair,
or somethin'?
Damn, you sure got skinny.
What's the matter?
Didn't they feed you in juvie?
Aw, shit! Kadota!
I hear you got hit
by a car, man!
You look okay to me, though.
Hot damn! Looks like I get
to kill you after all!
Uh-uh! I didn't say
you could come out yet!
[laughs] Sit tight.
The demolition show's
about to start!
[indistinct chatter]
Your fight's with me,
not with these guys.
What do you think I am,
an idiot?
Naw, man, you know
I ain't gonna let anyone go!
Punk bastard.
All right!
Yo, Walker!
How 'bout you--?
Hey. What the--?
That little bitch
ain't here. Huh?
Dude! No way,
it's Masaomi's piece of ass!
Holy shit, this day's
gettin' better and better!
[laughing] What are the odds
I'd run into all y'all tonight?
This is some
straight-up fate shit!
And I got Mikado
to thank for it!
[laughing]
What the hell
are you talkin' about?
Oh, that's right!
You don't know shit, do ya?
I ain't the boss
of the Blue Squares
anymore, bitch-face.
What?
You know that little pip-squeak,
Mikado Ryugamine?
He's our boss now,
asshole! [laughing]
I don't believe it.
It can't be true.
[both grunting]
[gun fires]
[groaning]
I bet you learned to shoot
reading how-to's online,
didn't ya?
I didn't think
you'd fire that thing
unless you had
both hands on it!
[groans]
You idiot!
You wanted us
to be part of this?
What's the goddamn point
if you're not with us?
Yeah, I ran away
from everything,
but Anri's been here
this whole time!
You ever think about her?
Ever think about how she feels?
And how you're
breaking her heart?
It doesn't matter
what I do, or say,
about the Dollars anymore.
So, now, I'm gonna end it.
Wait, what are you--?
[fires gun]
[screams]
What the hell you up to?
No good, as usual!
I just wanted to chat about
a problem called the Dollars.
[gasps]
I hear you hooked Mikado up
with a little
somethin'-somethin'.
I don't gotta say shit
to you, pal.
Aw, come on!
You don't have
to be like that.
Keepin' all the youngsters
in check's my job.
You know that.
I'll deal with the Dollars.
What, are you out
of your freakin' mind?
Let's talk
about your plan, then.
You were gonna
use these shootings
as an excuse to ice Mikado.
Then, you were gonna get
some punk you picked out
to take his place.
Set yourself up
with a nice new racket.
You don't know nothin'
about nothin'.
That kid dishonored
the old man,
takin' pot shots
at his place.
You think I'm gonna let
that shit slide?
I hear ya,
but I'd really appreciate it
if you let me handle this.
Why are you protecting
that son of a bitch?
Like you said,
I don't gotta say shit
to you, pal.
[scoffs]
Sir?
We just found out
the bullets were . 22 caliber.
[sighs]
You know what?
It looks like you and me
were barkin' up the wrong tree.
Huh?
The bullets they dug
out of the old man's place
and the cop shop
were small caliber.
Not the kinda shit I deal.
[groaning]
Cool, huh?
Some American terrorist
designed it years ago.
It fires if you push it
against something.
Handy, huh?
Hey, Nasujima?
I think Mikado just used
that gun I gave him.
[stammering]
What the goddamn hell
is he doing here?
Are you okay?
[stammering]
He's supposed to be in jail!
Break down the door
of that sushi place
and get your asses in there!
Find the guy
with the dreadlocks
and infect him!
Go on! Go!
I love you...
[grunting]
[screaming]
[growling]
[laughing]
[grunting]
[both screaming]
[men murmuring]
I hope I didn't keep you waiting
for too long, Mr. Izumii!
You bastard!
Ultimate move,
Walker Style, Innocentius!
[screaming]
Ashes to ashes!
Dust to dust!
I'm gonna kill you, Walker!
It's now or never, guys!
Go on, get yourselves
out of here, now!
But what about--?
Don't worry,
we can handle 'em!
[laughing]
That's a Death Flag
if I ever heard one!
It's okay, we got this.
You go find Mikado
and do what you do.
Okay.
[Walker]
You like it crispy?
How 'bout extra crispy?
Hey, they're gettin' aw--
[groans]
You shit-heels.
Y'all jacked up my van.
So, now, I'm gonna eat
your friggin' souls!
Oh, wow.
I can't believe I did it.
I shot you.
It was so easy,
like nothing.
If I can do that to you,
then what's to stop me
from shooting
someone else, like Anri?
And, if I can do that,
then I can do worse.
I could make everyone
around me suffer!
I can't let the Dollars
keep going,
and I can't let
myself, either!
Stop talking like you're--
You can't fix anything
by killing yourself, you pussy!
I've been thinking
about how bad I wanted
an extraordinary life,
how far I've had to go
to get it,
and what I have to do now
to stop my endless searching.
You don't have to do this!
You're being played!
Izaya's been playin' you
from he star!
I swear I'll kill him!
I'll kill him!
I'll make that bastard pay!
I swear it!
Even if it takes
the rest of my life!
Thank you. And sorry.
I know this'll sound weird,
but I'm kinda looking forward
to this next part.
Like, what if, after I die,
there's something else?
Then I'll get to go someplace
I've never seen before.
No! You don't have to!
Sorry, I do.
[Masaomi]
See what I mean?
Everything's gone to shit.
[gun fires]
Nobody's sicker of it than me.
[Mikado] The events
that changed destinies
and threw the city into chaos
are coming to an end.
We've all changed so much.
Where do we go next?
Is there anything left
to go back to?
Next time:
Those Who Meet Must Part.