[DUMMIES moaning]
[DUMMY 1]
It hurts!
[DUMMY 3]
Save us!
[DUMMY 4]
I'm hungry!
He he he he he he!
[DUMMY 1]
It hurts!
So you were saying
that the tests
aren't done yet...?
Well then, here is your test...
I'd say it's successful!
Undying... obedient...
invincible soldiers
who will fight whoever
we order them to.
We have our immortal legion...
at long last!
[DUMMY 5]
Pa... pa...?
Indeed...! Yes...!
I am your father, son!
And now...
I want you to listen closely...
there are many
renegade elements...
And they want to take us over.
Papa...
You men have a job to do.
[DUMMIES]
I-It hurts...
It hurts!
[ZAMPANO]
That's quite a doorway.
[DARIUS]
The air here seems foul.
You're sure this is it?
[ED]
Yeah.
It's exactly like Al told me.
[GERSO]
And who is this?!
[ED]
Number 66, Barry the Chopper...
One of the guardians
of the 5th Labratory...
[grunts; straining]
Oh, please...! Come on...!
Damn this stupid thing!
How do you open this?!
Stand back.
Oh...! Its open...huh?!
Order the Central
forces that are engaged
with Mustang and the
Briggs men to pull back.
What...? You're going to shoot?
Your subordinates are
lacking in discipline.
[OLIVIER]
Pull your forces back now...
My Briggs men will not
hesitate to wipe them out...
You don't want to lose
all of your troops, do you?
Close all the gates...!
Seal every entrance
to the command center!
Understand...?!
Don't let them in...!
No Briggs soldier or Mustang!
Ah... So you do
have some mettle,
twisted though it might be.
Oh, you shouldn't get too cocky.
We'll kill every
last one of you!
All you mountain savages!
Oh dear... Mess...
I made a mess.
You cannot... interfere...
See, I was told...
to kill you...
It's such a pain...
It looks like another
seat has just opened up...
Thanks, Homunculus...
You have my gratitude!
This sword was passed
through the Armstrong
family for generations.
Now I don't have to sully
it with his filthy blood.
You bastard!
So they don't die?!
[DUMMIES]
It hurts... So hungry.
It hurts... It hurts.
So hungry!
Big Brother!
[ED]
There's no way.
They used human souls
to make these things?!
[ZAMPANO]
Damn...They just keep coming...
What are these things?!
[DARIUS]
How should I know...?!
And why won't they die?!
[SCAR]
This is bad...
If thse things
escape outside....
Looks like something major.
Yeah.
Word is, Mustang's
leading a coup d'état.
This won't turn out pretty.
There, there, now sweetie.
Please don't cry.
Now what?
[GERSO]
Get off!!
Oh no!
They're starting to get out!
Sorry...
I guess I just cut off our exit.
Don't worry about it...
If you hadn't done it,
I would've slammed the
damn thing shut myself.
And now we can really
take these guys on.
Yeah, you said it, Zampano...!
Now that all these things
are trapped here with us,
we can really show our stuff.
This is gonna be good!
How could they even think
to create these monsters?
Well, it looks like
we'll just have to
plow through them
so we can get at
that bearded bastard!
Let's take these things down!
[OFFICER 4] Mustang is fleeing
in an ice cream truck...!
Seal off the main roads!
The vehicle is disguised
as a civilian truck,
but it's loaded with weapons...
Be on the lookout!
[OFFICER 4]
A-A bear! A bear with a Mohawk!
They cut out.
A bear with a Mohawk...?
[MARIA]
That's...odd...
[HAWKEYE] That sounds
like Captain Buccaneer.
Colonel...
I think it's going to be
hard to get into town.
Sounds like it.
So, they're looking for
an ice cream truck, huh?
[HEINKEL] I wonder if the
others are doing all right.
It's aggravating not being
able to fight with them...
Who knew that sitting around
waiting could be so painful?
[tap, tap, tap]
I've been hearing that
damn sound since yesterday...
Hey Alphonse, what's
all that racket in there?
[AL] Selim's been
playing with my head.
[tap, tap, tap]
Whatever else he might be...
he's still just a little kid.
[tap, tap, tap]
Stop him, Alphonse!
Stop him from
making that sound...!
"Dot-dot-dash!"...
It's code-- he's
sending out a signal!
[tap, tap, tap]
He's been broadcasting
our location!
Ahhh!!!
[explosion]
[SELIM]
Hey.
Thank you for coming
to get me, Kimblee...
I appreciate it.
Yeah, I'm here...
But please don't give me
any more extra work to do.
I'm sorry about
all the trouble...
I won't let my guard down again.
[NARRATOR]
Fullmetal Alchemist.
Ahhhhh!!!
What's going on, Envy?
It looks like
you tricked me!
No! I didn't lie to you!
Your search for immortality
ends further inside.
Keep going!
You little brat!
I'm back!
I'm alive again!
Ha ha ha ha!!!
Thanks for getting me
this far, little squirt...
So kind of you...
Very... kind.
What are these
soldiers doing here?
Do you think they're
gonna evict us?
But what would we do?
There's no other place
that we could go to.
[YOKI]
W-What's happening...?
Do you think they caught
wind of where we are?
Not good. We have to tell Al--
Wait, please hold on!
What happens if
somebody discovers
that you're Dr. Marcoh?
I don't care...!
We can't just sit
here and do nothing!
Just calm down.
Think about it.
If you're taken
prisoner or something,
it's just going to be that
much harder on Alphonse!
See what I'm saying?
We can't afford...
to move carelessly...
Right...? Right?
Ah, so you're alone, then...?
I had thought that
Gluttony was out here
with you as well.
Yes, well, in the end
I had to consume him.
You ate Gluttony?
Your own kind?
It's not like it's
cannibalism...
We are a collective.
We were both born
of the same father.
And now we've gone
back to being one form.
[KIMBLEE]
So that's how it works, huh?
[AL]
Mr. Heinkel!
Oh... Still alive?
What a pity for you.
But then, you
are a chimera...
The life force
is strong in you.
[AL]
Mr. Heinkel!
Damn it! Let me go!
You're not going anywhere.
[AL]
Why... you...
Why bother fighting?
Crash!!
Why bother running?
What's that?
Hmph...
I should've known
that wouldn't work.
[OFFICER 6] That's far
enough, General Armstrong!
We have our orders,
and we're prepared
to shoot you
for the traitor you are!
Take aim, men...! Fire!
You idiot!
You shouldn't have
concentrated your men!
[thinking] Please tell me
that at least did something!
Hey, look... I... caught you.
And this time...
I won't mess... up.
Must kill her...
the woman general.
Hello, Sister...!
Are you all right?
Who do you think I am...?
Of course I'm all right!
I'm just glad to see
that you're okay...
Now then, could you tell me...
what the hell that is?
[OLIVIER]
A Homunculus...
Bullets don't work on him.
Maybe if we had
some heavy artillery...
You don't say...
Fortunately, dear sister,
that is my specialty...
Why don't you let your
brother have a crack at it...?
I'll take this atrocity down.
Come on... you monster!
What a... pain...
Just leave me...
Get out of here.
Listen to me...!
Go...! Quickly!
[AL]
No way!
Don't talk back to me...!
At this rate, we'll both die.
Leave me behind...
You might be able
to save yourself!
[AL]
I told you--not happening!
Now think about
something useful instead...
Like staying alive!
[HEINKEL]
You dumbass!
Think about it...
We're facing
Kimblee and Pride both.
Now leave me
here and get moving!
[AL]
Don't give up...!
I swear...I'll save you!
Oh no!
Come on, legs...! Move it!
We've come too far!
We can't afford
to be beaten now!
I won't let it happen.
Mr. Heinkel... grab on!
We're not giving up!
You brothers... are
really something else.
You're still determined
to help another person...
even when you're falling
to pieces yourself.
[AL]
I promised...
I promised my brother...
I wouldn't let anyone
else die, no matter what.
I guess you're right...
Wasn't it Kimblee who said
that the true test of
winning was surviving?
Which reminds me,
I have something
that might be useful.
Mr. Heinkel, why
do you have that?
I happened to pick it up...
I got it when Kimblee
abandoned us in the mine.
[AL]
A Philosopher's Stone...
With this we might actually
have a chance at winning...
But--
[HEINKEL]
Yeah, I know...
These are made using
human lives, aren't they?
Your brother told me...
He said you'd rather not use
one of these to get your
original bodies back...
In that case...
don't use it for yourself...
use it to save the
entire world instead.
You deserve it,
because even though they've
been put into that stone,
you still recognize
them as people.
I know... those people...
even though they're
trapped in stone...
they still want
to fight to protect
what matters to them.
Let them fight...
They deserve the chance.
[AL]
All right.
Now, you give them hell for me.
Alphonse!
[AL]
We'll fight... together!
[KIMBLEE]
This dust cloud is a nuisance...
Shall I blow it away
with a blast wave?
No.
The two of them
are still trapped
somewhere in the
bowels of the cloud...
And without his legs,
how can he possibly escape?
Ah, well, what do you know...
He isn't exactly running.
Good!
[KIMBLEE]
There you are.
Very well done,
Alphonse Elric...!
[NARRATOR] If you're fighting
a battle, person to person...
you must have a
plan and follow it...
If you hesitate because
you fear to fail...
you are nothing
more than a fool.
Next time, on Fullmetal
Alchemist: Brotherhood...
Episode Fifty-Two:
"Combined Strength."
The time for
ambivalence is long past.