Time has passed since the
devastating war between
humans and monsters
came at last to an end.
People have sought to secure
survival and prosperity
by harnessing the primeval
power known as aer.
When crystallized,
aer is formed into cores...
These cores, in turn,
are used to power "blastia."
We use many different types
of cores to create and power
a variety of blastia...
It is thanks to these that we
continue to live and to prosper.
Magic and monsters...
In this world ruled by powers
beyond human understanding,
we are faced continuously with
difficult decisions to make.
What should we protect...?
What should we give up...?
How should we live our lives?
Hold on! You're going to fast!
Pick up the pace, then.
Yuri...! Over here!
Done here. Next one!
How many are we setting?
Our team's got three.
Over here!
Come on, Flynn.
Right!
Don't go falling behind!
Do you think the other teams
are going to make it?
Slow it down. We have
to stick to the plan.
You can't just barge ahead
'cause you feel like it!
It's not like we have
time to wait around.
They're gaining on us.
Go on!
All yours!
All right!
Nobody mentioned
these guys to me...
Guess I'll improvise.
Okay, Yuri, we're all set here.
Now let's get going!
Where did those
things come from?
Has the operation failed?
No... I think we should
just keep on going.
Glad we rushed.
None of the other teams
are even here yet.
Will you shut up?
Everything's going
according to plan.
You can't talk to me like that!
Now I'm a little scared.
Wow! There are a ton of them.
Back that way.
Took you long enough.
Whoa, look over there.
What the hell is happening?
What now?
Chastel...! Everyone's here.
Hurry! Do something, Hisca!
Yurgis, quick...!
Get those two back here!
Yuri! Flynn! Fall back now!
Here we go.
O brilliant light,
be as a wall to allay arms.
Force Field!
Is it over?
Think so.
Yuri!
Flynn!
Your first job is over...
Not too shabby!
Yuri!
What's wrong this time?
What do you think is wrong?
Why didn't you
stick to the plan?
What's the big deal?
It all worked out
in the end, right?
We're in this together.
Your recklessness affects
every one of us, not just you.
Oh please, get off
my case already.
You're as fussy as an old lady.
And you're as
responsible as a toddler.
Enough, you two.
Shut up and calm down.
Go take care of the clean-up.
No more squabbling!
Yes, Sir.
Great, thanks to you
I've got a bump on my head.
Me? It was your fault.
Shut up!
Captain!
What is it, Lambert?
It seems the red trees
are approaching the town
more and more rapidly, sir.
Yeah...
The aer...
Are you ever planning to
put your full uniform on?
Yes, Mom, I'm going to
put it on in a minute...
You're such a stickler.
It's getting old.
And look at this floor!
Get off my back!
Talk about bad luck...
Getting assigned not
only to the same post,
but the same room as you...
Someone definitely
has it out for me.
Trust me, the
feeling is mutual...
I still don't get why you even
joined the Knights at all.
Boys, I'm coming in.
How can you not be ready yet?
It's time to go.
I'm sorry.
So hurry.
The town's so deserted,
and it's only been a month.
It was bad for business when
the monsters started appearing.
You guys are late.
I left Chris behind to wait.
Your shift's up next.
Yes sir.
Yuri...
Don't go running off on your
own like yesterday, all right?
Hey! Come back here
and say that again!
Seriously?!
Do you have to cause
trouble everywhere you go?
It's just his natural charm.
Shut up...!
Nobody thinks you're funny...
Ugh... this furball's annoying.
Be nice. Repede's
yours to look after.
I'm bored. Why don't you
show me your magic artes?
What...? But there's no
real need for it right now.
I didn't see it yesterday.
I was face-down in the dirt...
and they won't give us
rookies any blastia.
I don't think they'll
ever give you any.
With your connections,
I'm guessing you'll
get yours quickly...
Your father was one of the
Knights, too, now wasn't he?
Anything I get
I'll earn for myself.
Just show me.
We can call it education.
I'm not showing you anything
until you ask nicely.
Please... just... show...
me... damn... it.
That's not going to cut it.
That's it...?
That's pretty lame.
We specialize in healing
and defense artes.
Come here, Chastel!
This is another way
you can use blastia
to make it more powerful.
Hey... what are you doing?
That could've been dangerous.
Captain!
What are you doing here?
Checking the forest.
Now quit standing
around and go patrol!
Yes, Sir.
Hey, Captain...!
Take this with you.
I'm afraid it isn't very much,
since we can't go hunting
in the forest these days.
Yeah, I'm sorry about that.
We'll have it safe again
as soon as possible.
All right, I'm going
to see Garista ...
You guys are on your own.
Yes, Sir.
Oh, uh, Captain...!
Would you take Repede
with you? He's a nuisance.
Go on, Lambert.
See you later.
Yeah.
Hey...! I've got what
you asked for, Captain.
Great... Toss it down.
Thanks a bunch.
He's so buddy-buddy with them...
The Knights in the capital
would never be so informal.
It's all part of
small town life...
We all gotta work
together around here.
Still... he's not a
typical Knight captain...
That makes it easier.
What's he thinking...?
Make the forest safe soon?
He promises them too much!
Garista!
Good afternoon, Captain Fedrok.
Same to you, Garista.
I would appreciate it
if you kept your voice
down in the library.
Come on. I want your
opinion on something.
So, you're doing
well in the forest...
Most of the monsters
have been subdued.
Yes, thanks mainly
to your strategy.
One thing...
While in the forest,
we noticed an
unusual amount of aer.
It's making the plants
and animals crazy.
Then you believe aer is behind
the sudden surge
in monster activity?
And the unseasonal red foliage?
Not just that.
Our blastia acted up a little
during the mission, too.
That's troubling indeed.
And your hypothesis is
that there is so much aer
spewing out that it's
affecting the blastia.
Yeah. There won't be
much point in trying to
clear out the monsters
unless we can stop it.
Do you have any idea
where it's coming from?
You know those ruins
in the lake upriver...?
Seeing as the red trees
lead off in that direction,
I'm thinking there
might be something there
we should look into.
And whatever this
"something" is,
you believe that it's
releasing the aer.
Interesting...
Some sort of blastia, perhaps?
Those old ruins have been
abandoned for many years...
Any sort of activity
would be strange...
We will need to
investigate quickly.
A mandate arrived today
from the capital...
It says you're to attend
the ceremony to celebrate
the tenth anniversary
of the Great War's end.
It isn't a Knight's
duty to stand around
dressed all formal
and twiddle his thumbs.
That's a difficult thing
to explain to Headquarters.
If you're going to
attend the ceremony,
you'll need to leave soon.
Yeah, yeah...
Anyway, do you know
anybody who's an expert
on aer or blastia?
Let's see... Actually, I do.
I believe there's
a blastia researcher
named Rita Mordio who
has a laboratory nearby.
Good. Where is it?
What about the ceremony...?
It's in three days.
I'll send somebody else.
His Excellency ordered it.
I deem this far more urgent...
It's my first priority.
Fine... if you insist...
but I think there's one
more thing you should know.
The researcher I told you about
can be a bit
difficult to deal with.
I'd suggest bringing
a gift along for her.
Man, I'm glad the shift's over.
It's exhausting. I feel like
I'm always on-edge lately.
Well then, I have an idea.
What's this great idea?
We should stop by here later.
No thanks. I think I'll pass.
Too good to hang out with us?
He can be such a prude.
Oh, no. This place is
filled with guild men.
This is just our luck.
Guild men? What are
you talking about?
I'm sure you had them
in the lower quarter, too.
They act like vigilantes,
but all they really care
about is making money...
They're part of a larger
group called the Union,
which is led by Don Whitehorse.
Basically, they're
a nasty bunch.
Yuri, come back here!
See, this guy wanted safe
passage all the way to
the town on the other
side of the forest...
So I told him, "Alright,
but you're gonna have to
give me all your
money up front."
Don't even think about it.
Welcome!
We'll have two Mabo Curries...
oh... and some milk, please.
Oh, isn't he adorable?
Is this little guy
a member, too?
He hasn't been
officially enlisted yet.
I'll be back in just a minute.
Thanks...
It was a real pain
in the ass, though,
so I kept all the money
and ditched him
the minute we got
outta the forest.
You were supposed to escort
him all the way to town.
That wasn't very nice of you.
Scamming people
out of their money
and then using it
to booze it up.
You're a real prince,
aren't you?
Yo... You got some
spunk, huh, Mr. Knight?
How about you say that
again, to my face?
You lowlife thugs are all alike.
You guys are a dime a dozen.
Eh?!
Could you lean back a bit?
I'm not looking for a boyfriend.
You little punk.
Come on...
Come on, Flynn... Do something.
I'm staying right here.
Yuri's the one who
started it all...
It has nothing to do with--
Hey, kid. You think
you're some big shot?
I said I don't want
to be part of this!
Hey!
And who the hell are you?
Bastard!
That is enough!
What was going through your head
when you dared draw
a blade in here?
But... but you see, sir...
Very sorry, sir.
You've got balls...
Too bad you decided to
become a dog of the Empire.
I'm Merzhom Keida...
The man in charge of
the guild in this town.
Yuri... Yuri Lowell.
Nice to meet you.
Work's all but
dried up lately...
It's got all of my men
a bit high-strung.
From now on I'll make sure
they see every job through...
Given that assurance,
I hope you can excuse their
reprehensible behavior.
No problem... It's excused.
There's something abnormal
about these monsters
we've been seeing
around here lately.
Yeah.
For one thing,
they never used to go
anywhere near towns
that had barriers.
So what's Niren doing about it?
Niren...?
Oh... You mean the captain.
So you guys are on
a first-name basis?
Yeah, it's a long, boring story.
I hear you guys had
a large scale mission
in the forest yesterday,
hunting down monsters.
Yeah.
The trees are
unseasonably red, too.
Seems likely there's some sort
of connection there, doesn't it?
I don't know...
But the captain sure does seem
to think there is, though.
He's consulting with
our strategist about it.
That's enough.
Keep your big mouth shut!
Idiot!
We're leaving!
Ow, ow, ow!
Hey, I'm not done eating yet!
Let go...! Come on
guys, this hurts!
Okay! Okay!
Hey Raven!
I've got a little job for you.
No fair...! You're using
healing artes on him...
I should get them, too!
Shut up!
Maybe the pain will
teach you a lesson.
I do feel sorry for you,
getting injured like this...
but only a little bit sorry.
I'm older than you!
Oh, no! It looks like you
got a head injury, too...
Let me see.
Just hold still.
I don't get it.
Why would someone like you
join the Knights
in the first place?
Why wouldn't I?
I mean the pay is
decent and it's not like
I have anything else to do...
Besides, I'm a great fighter.
In other words, before,
he was just wandering around
aimlessly hoping to
find somebody to fight...
--Right, Yuri?
--Shut up!
He's always been like this:
immature and reckless.
Oh, like you've changed at all.
You're still uptight
and judgmental.
You're childhood friends?
We both grew up in the lower
quarter of the capital...
That's all.
Man, it was like
a dream come true
when you finally moved away.
And then you had to
go and spoil it all
by showing up for the
recruitment exam...
Why did you really join?
Who knows?
it's possible your old man
rubbed off on me or something...
I always thought he
was a great guy...
and, not having any
parents of my own,
maybe I was a little
jealous of you.
Don't talk about him, okay?
Hey, you four.
Go in and see the captain when
you're finished up out here.
He's not happy.
Why would the captain
be mad at us?
We didn't do anything wrong.
In case you've
already forgotten,
we're members of the Knights
and there's this little
thing called "discipline."
He's going to think I'm
an incompetent bozo...!
This is just perfect!
Brawling in a pub.
That's one stupidity you
could have easily avoided.
I'm very sorry, sir.
Things are already crazy
enough outside of town...
There's no need to stir up
more trouble inside.
But those guild men were
totally out of line, Captain!
This guy told an old man he'd
protect him, took his money,
and then just ditched him...
I had to teach them a lesson!
That's what started it...
Well... I probably would've
done the same thing... Still...
The guilds are
autonomous groups,
free from imperial influence.
They're not entirely
despicable men.
I find that hard
to believe, sir.
In case you haven't
already realized it,
they're handling some
things that we don't have
the resources to deal with.
For a price, of course.
The guy who's leading
them is called Merzhom.
It seemed like he knew you.
Hmm...? Merzhom...
Yeah, well, that's
a long, boring story.
It's not like that!
We're not doing business
under the table or anything!
Are you all fixed up?
Yes, sir.
Then go back to your
quarters... We're done here.
Huh?
So... you're not tossing
us in the stockade?
What would that do other
than decrease our manpower?
Still, I should do something...
Letting the four of you
completely off the hook
would set a bad example
for the others...
Tell you what, I'll just
have the pub's repair costs
deducted from your pay.
Oh, and Flynn...
I'm going to send
you to the capital.
Sir?
You'll be filling in for me.
I will?!
There's something more
important I need to see to...
Yurgis'll be in charge
here while I'm gone...
You'll be attending an
official ceremony...
and delivering this request
for reinforcements.
I'm convinced there's
something going on
in those ruins near the lake...
and if I'm right, we'll need
more manpower to handle it...
Oh! I'll also need to bring
one'a you twins with me.
I'll take the bigger one.
Does he mean our...?
Yeah, I think he does.
"Bigger one"?
Well they look like the exact
same height to me... Right?
As for you, Yuri: you'll
be looking after Lambert.
Again with the dogs?!
Yuri.
Yeah, what now?
Quit causing trouble.
I'm tired of getting
dragged into it.
Yeah, yeah...
You're a member of
the Knights, now...
You have to obey the rules.
You need to be more responsible.
And if that's too much
for you to handle
then you don't belong here.
I still don't see how anything
I did tonight was wrong.
If you can't swallow your
pride and learn to obey orders,
you should leave the Knights.
I am done talking to you.
Ow!
We're lost, aren't we?
Yeah, pretty much.
Can you read this?
How could anyone call
all these scribbles a map?
That's weird. Sir Garista
is usually so precise.
Chastel! Look over there!
Looks like some kinda
alarm... Check it out.
Right.
Thataway!
The capital.
This is a laboratory?
Apparently so...
Hey...! 'Scuse me,
is anyone here?
Get lost. Leave me alone.
Hold on!
Thieves! Go away!
She's just going back to sleep?
A kid?
Rita Mordio, yes...?
My name is Niren Fedrok,
and this is Chastel Aiheap.
We're with the
Imperial Knights...
and this right here is
our bargaining chip.
Yeah, alright. What
do you want to know?
We've detected a
large amount of aer
being produced in the
forest near Ceazontania...
So much, in fact, it's affecting
plants and normally
gentle animals in the area.
I dunno, it seems
pretty unlikely that aer
could produce those kinds
of effects all by itself.
So that means...?
Hey, hold on a second...
Ceazontania, huh?
Yes, there are some ruins
in the lake upstream.
Ah, I know where
you're talking about.
I've scoped that place before.
But the barrier blastia
that I found in place there
was missing its core.
So, does that mean the
blastia isn't active?
Nope. And from what I saw,
I'm pretty sure there wasn't
an aer krene there, either.
What's an aer krene?
It's a little bit like a spring,
but made of aer
instead of water.
Aer flows through the land,
so you can find it
pretty much anywhere...
but there are some places
where it really gushes out.
But in this case...
if it's suddenly producing
large amounts of aer,
it's possible somebody inserted
a core into the blastia
to activate it.
Maybe the blastia
is out of control,
and it's spewing out
large amounts of aer.
Everybody knows
blastia are useful for
generating all kinds of power...
but if they're being
used improperly,
they can be
incredibly dangerous.
So then, let's assume
this blastia is active.
Would it be possible
for us to destroy it?
I can't really say without
knowing what kind of core it is.
There has to be
something we can do.
This aer... is it red?
Yeah.
Too concentrated...
If oversaturation is affecting
the surrounding area,
then the only option is to
stop it at its source somehow.
Just a minute.
Here.
I built this little
one to collect aer...
She might be able
to clear things up.
How does it work?
You just set her
down and activate her
near the source of the aer...
She's programmed to take care
of everything else on her own.
I can't guarantee that
she'll be helpful, though...
She is a blastia, after all...
She could easily
be affected, too.
And this is just a theory
you came up with on the fly.
Right. It's just a theory.
Thanks for the help.
Perfect! I've been looking
everywhere for this core!
Hey, how'd you know
where to find me, anyway?
Garista, one of my men, told me.
Figures it was that guy...
I really can't
stand that weasel.
You know each other well?
No way...! I only met
him in the capital...
The guy is a jerk!
Are you sure?
Heck yeah!
He took the cores I found
and turned them into weapons.
Like I said-- a jerk.
The stupid Empire only sees
blastia as tools for war...
but they're so much
more than that!
Just a sec.
Here, take this with you...
It's a special formula
that'll make your blastia
immune to the aer's effects.
What do you mean,
immune to the aer's effects?
It'll keep them from overloading
due to the increased
concentration of aer.
It won't last long, though.
If you're going to
check this thing out,
you should probably hurry.
If the blastia
goes out of control,
it could take out the town,
not just the ruins.
Think of it this way:
blastia has the power
to protect the city...
so the opposite is
just as possible.
Thank you.
Appreciate the help.
This core is all
the thanks I need!
Uh, out of curiosity, do you
live out here by yourself?
This is just the
laboratory where I work...
I live somewhere
else entirely...
Shut the door, will ya?
Oookay.
Your Excellency
Commandant Alexei...
the Council has a request.
They ask that the Lady Estellise
be allowed to attend
the upcoming ceremony.
Again?
They claim the celebration
is meaningless without her,
as she may be the
successor to the throne.
Successor?
She is merely the Council's
nominee... Nothing more.
The Council is not to have
contact with Lady Estellise...
Is that clear?
Yes, sir.
Your Excellency...!
A messenger from
Ceazontania has arrived.
Ceazontania?
I am Flynn Scifo of the
Ceazontania brigade...
I have come to the
capital to attend
the ceremony as Captain
Niren Fedrok's proxy.
Why does he not come himself?
Inside that case you will find
a document requesting
reinforcements.
All officers ranked
captain or higher
were to attend this ceremony.
That was the order I gave.
Excellency...!
Strange things have
been happening...
There's abnormal aer in
the forest near town...
Monsters are appearing!
Please sir...
I beg you, read the request.
When is the ceremony rehearsal?
It will begin shortly, sir.
Wait...! Your Excellency!
I will dispatch reinforcements
after the ceremony...
Until then, you're on your own.
The situation is most dire...
The citizens are
in serious danger.
Remember your place, Knight...!
Boy... your only job right
now is to convey my orders
back to Fedrok.
Return at once...
I will not have a Knight of
your rank attend this ceremony.
It's Flynn... Flynn Scifo...?
Would that make you
the son of Finath Scifo?
From what I hear, you passed
the Knight's recruitment exam
with flying colors...
I'm sure your father'd be proud
to see you following
in his steps.
My father...
I hope you aren't planning
to follow his example
and throw your life away...
Don't forget: you're a
member of the Knights now.
Flynn...
Lady Estellise...
Good to see you again.
It was noble of you to come
all the way from Ceazontania...
I pray for the safety
of the citizens there.
Thank you, my lady.
The imperial capital
is maintaining
a precarious
balance right now...
I know it's a lot to ask of
your brigade, but please...
hang on a little longer.
I'm glad it's me the
captain sent in his place...
I'm sure Yuri would have slugged
His Excellency in a heartbeat.
Yuri...? Who is he?
He's...
Well, then...
Please be careful.
He's made a mess of things.
I want this taken care of.
Yes, Sir!
See...?
I told you that taking out
monsters in the forest
would be way more fun
than stupid training.
And I told you, not until
the reinforcements arrive.
Never seen anything
like that before.
The barrier will
protect the town.
Now let's get going!
Into town, hurry!
Now, Kansuke...!
Fall back inside the town!
Leave it, Elvin.
We're falling back!
Yuri...! That's enough!
Time to retreat!
My daughter...
She's in the carriage...! Emma!
Emma!
We're gonna go see
your mommy now, okay?
Let's go, Lambert.
You lead the way!
Let's get the injured back
inside the town. Hurry up!
Mommy!
Emma... Oh, my baby!
Yuri, fall back into town!
Come on! Hurry!
Sure about this...?
There isn't any
money in it for you.
Don't worry about it.
I'll send the bill to your boss.
--Argus! Come back!
--John!
Where are you going?
What is it, Lambert?
Come back here...! Now, Lambert!
Yuri!
Anyone who can, come!
Damn...! All right,
you two... let's follow them.
Damn it...
His tracks are all mixed
in with the monsters'.
Lambert!
Lambert...! Argus!
The aer's getting even
thicker here than it was before.
You mean... this is aer?
Normally, aer is green...
but it seems that it turns red
when it's unusually
thick like this.
So is this what's makin'
all the trees wither
and the animals get violent...?
Aer's keeping us
outta the forest?
Well?
Yes... We believe
that to be the case.
No point in keeping it under
wraps anymore, now is there?
Help me!
After 'em!
Merzhom!
Yuri, get back here!
Unbelievable!
Guards up, everyone.
Damn it all...
Something that dangerous
this close to town?
Things are getting
worse than I thought.
It's Lambert!
Hold up a second.
Lambert, no...
Lambert, what are you doing?
Stop, please! Get off me!
Stop... Please stop,
Lambert... Don't do this.
Lambert!
My friend... I'm sorry.
Dammit!
Oh, Repede... I'm so sorry...
Your dad--I had no other choice.
What in the world happened?
The monsters made it all
the way to the bridge.
Hisca, what's the matter?
What happened...?
Talk to me...! Hisca!
Lambert and the other dogs...
They just turned
into monsters...
Then they all...
And Yuri... he...
Hisca...
I heard what happened.
You should keep an extra
close eye on Repede.
I bet he's gonna feel
a bit lonely for a while.
I'm sorry, Captain.
There's nothing you
need to apologize for.
Now, why don't you
head back to your room?
Try not to catch cold.
No! Please!
I'm gettin' too old
for this stuff...
Need a breather.
What's somebody doin'
out here this late?
No, it's the truth...!
We tried to use magic artes,
and our blastia just exploded.
Explodin' blastia?!
That's a Royal Guard.
Who's that he's talkin' to?
Damn!
What's this?!
Thank you... I'll take
charge of the report now.
Things are startin' ta get
a little bit
complicated around here.
Mister Knight!
Here, take this.
You saved me...
Thank you so much!
Flynn...
Nice, cushy job you got,
taking care of the dogs.
What?
I've got a cushy job, huh...?
I'm sure it was
real tough for you,
standing around
at the ceremony.
Get outta my way...
I'm too busy for you.
And it must be nice
getting pampered
just because your daddy
was a Knight, too, huh?
Screw you...
I guess being a jerk's the
one thing you're good at!
How many times am I gonna
see you two in here like this?
Now go hit the baths. You
stink... We'll talk after that.
How can you be so relaxed with
everything that's happening...?
We have to do something!
We can't for now.
He's not sending anybody...
not till after the ceremony.
His orders are for us
to hold the fort...
I'll bring the
documents to you later.
I see... Very well.
Did you even explain everything
that's been going on here?!
Yes! I can't help whatever
Headquarters decides to do!
Wait until after the ceremony?
So what, we sit around
and do nothing?!
Don't you think I said
the same thing...?!
They just don't see
us as a priority...!
There's nothing we can do!
People have died, Flynn!
I suppose you think I
didn't try hard enough?
Quit your arguing.
Sounds like I gave you
an unpleasant task, Flynn.
That was inconsiderate.
I apologize.
You're sorry?!
The situation is
only worsening...
We won't be able to keep
the town safe and secure
if the monsters attack again.
So tomorrow we'll
investigate the ruins.
Sir, you can't be serious...
If we do that, then people
are going to die...!
We can't just disobey an order--
Thinking of your old man?
Yeah, I am...
He liked ignoring orders, too...
Headquarters had stopped
the attack, but he...
Have you forgotten that people
in the lower quarter were dying?
He died protecting
citizens and his family.
My father died disobeying
the orders he was given...!
Did you know they
never found his body?
I am never going to make the
same mistake that my father did.
Our job is to protect the
people who live in this town.
That's my duty as a Knight,
and I take it very seriously...
Flynn... Maybe you
should wait until
you've served as a Knight
for a little longer...
Then you can decide if
what your old man did
was really a mistake or a
commitment to sacred duty.
We leave first thing in
the morning... Understood?
Garista... Inform
the others, would you?
Yes, Sir.
Sorry about earlier...
I didn't know that
Lambert had died.
No, I'm sorry...
I was just shocked that
they refused us outright.
My father's body never
got a proper burial.
They only gave us a
few personal effects.
Once you die, it's over...
Everything ends...
and there's nothing left,
nothing that matters.
The monsters are practically
on our doorstep...
What if they get
inside the town?
What do we do then?
The barrier's still there...
They'll have a hard time
getting past that, at least.
Maybe, but I'm still
with the captain on this.
The whole reason we
asked for reinforcements
was because it was too
much for us to handle...
We should wait.
If we don't do something,
more people will die...
I've seen enough death...
I'm ready to start
fighting back.
If we die, then
who protects them?
I'm going down to see Repede.
Maybe you should reconsider...
There's still time
to change your mind.
The ceremony will
end tomorrow...
Wouldn't it be wise to wait?
You have any idea
how long it'll take 'em
to assemble a unit
and get 'em here?
Even so...
Besides, I'd prefer to
have all this taken care of
before Alexei's men arrive.
Why is that?
I hear he's really
interested in blastia...
If there's a powerful
one in the ruins,
he might order us to bring
it back in working condition
instead of destroying it.
It's wreaking havoc with the aer
and turning even our trained
animals into monsters.
Everyone took a hit in
this latest attack...
Citizens, Knights,
even livestock...
I don't want any
more casualties.
It's as simple as that.
Yes, I understand...
I'll determine a route for you.
Thanks...
One more thing...
I'm concerned about
taking blastia with us.
I'm worried that
this unusual aer
might interfere
with them somehow.
Surely not having
their magic artes
will affect the squad's
morale on the mission.
As much as we know,
we still don't have total
control of the way in which
cores provide
blastia with energy.
I'm sure they just activated
a little late last time.
Fine then... We'll take 'em,
but I hope you're right.
It's Yuri.
Yeah... It's open, come in.
What's up?
Not much. I just...
couldn't sleep.
Doesn't sound like you.
Yeah...
Here. A glass of
grape juice for you.
Thank you.
So, is that your
wife and daughter?
Oh, yeah...
They're not with
us anymore, though.
There was an incident...
I wasn't able to protect them.
Back then, I totally
bought into the idea
that the Empire's
orders were absolute...
Even when acting
against those orders
might have saved the lives
of my wife and little girl.
Anyway, a lot
happened after that,
and they shipped me off
to the middle of nowhere.
I actually kinda
like it out here...
being so far away
from the capital.
It sure is biting us in
the ass now, though...
but still I'm
determined not to make
the same mistakes
I did in the past.
Flynn's old man was
really somethin'...
Wasn't always the
most positive guy...
But I had a lot of
respect for him...
Now there was a man
who knew how to protect
what was most dear to him.
Yes?
I know it's quite late...
and I'm sorry to bother you.
What is it, sir?
Won't you sit down?
No... thank you...
We're leaving early tomorrow.
You don't seem to agree
with this mission...
Unless I'm mistaken.
I'm a member of
the Knights, sir...
My personal feelings
don't really matter.
I must admit,
I'm a little troubled
by Captain Fedrock's
decision as well...
I don't understand
why he insists
on putting the
brigade in danger.
I agree... We should
obey Headquarters...
protect the townfolk...
and wait for reinforcements
before taking any action.
That's quite sensible...
You don't take after
your father, then.
You see...
I didn't know him well, but I
did meet him once, before...
Captain Fedrok's actions
actually remind me a lot
of something your late
father would have done.
Anyway, His Excellency's
orders are absolute...
Captain Fedrock has an
obligation to obey orders
just as your father did.
So tell me, Flynn...
Knowing it will be an act of
insubordination on your part...
are you still going?
I am a member of the Knights...
I will obey my
direct superior...
I may not fully agree with
what the captain's doing...
but he said something
to me earlier,
and I want to find
out what it means.
Good night, sir.
What a shame...
If things had
gone the other way,
he might have made a fine
servant for His Excellency.
Goodness. Are you
all right out here?
Tonight I'm drinkin' fer
me and my dead buddy.
Round two!
I think you should go home.
Let's go back.
When we depart from here,
we will follow the river
and enter the ruins on the lake.
Once there, we will
investigate...
We will identify and
then resolve the cause
of the aer disturbance.
I'd prefer to wait
for reinforcements,
but this matter is too urgent.
If the effects of the aer
remain unchecked any longer,
the town will be in
even greater danger.
It's our duty to
protect these people!
So... uhhh...
everyone ready to go?
Yuri...
Hey, what's wrong little one?
Why are you up so early?
You guys are going somewhere
dangerous, aren't you?
Now, where'd you hear that...?
Don't you worry...
I showed you how tough I am.
Uh, Captain...
Ah, c'mon.
There's no need for
so many long faces.
We'll just be gone
for a little bit.
All you have to do
is wait for us
and don't step
outside the barrier.
Just hang on a little longer.
Life will be back
to normal soon.
'Kay, let's go.
That's just plain reckless.
They don't even know
what they're up against.
Makes me wonder why I bothered
to warn 'em in
the first place...
but that's Niren for ya...
Now that I think on it,
havin' 'em owe us one
doesn't sound half bad.
You're not serious?
You seriously need
to report to the Don.
Now, get outta here.
Yeah, yeah...!
Well... you take care.
What is it, sir?
Hey, Yurgis...
will you do me a favor and
give your blastia a try?
Sure.
What's happening?
It's because of the aer here.
So you're saying we can't
use our blastia at all?
Well... that's where
these come in...
They're formulas to help keep
the blastia from overloading...
I made enough copies
for everybody.
They don't last long, though,
so you'll only want to
use them as a last resort.
You knew our blastia
would go out of control
before we even left?
Correct... Like I said,
the situation is urgent...
It would be a disaster if
the town's Barrier Blastia
went haywire, too...
Now, let's get moving.
And you're only
telling us all this now?!
It might've been helpful if
you'd said something sooner!
Whoops... Guess I forgot.
Huh?
He forgot to mention it...?
Are we really letting
this guy lead us?
Shut up and move it...! Now!
Well, I guess this explains
something, at least...
Why we haven't
run into monsters.
This place makes my skin crawl.
Are we gonna end up down
there like that, too?
Keep your guards up...
There's no telling
what might happen.
Frozen Arrows, ready! Quick!
Don't hit David...! Fire!
Pull him out!
Get away from the swamp, now!
Hurry!
That monster back there
detected our presence.
I'm guessing that it reacts
to sound and sudden movement.
Going forward, we'll split
ourselves into two teams...
One will cross the bridge
and enter the ruins.
The other will give support.
The support team will
provide sufficient cover
all the way to the entrance,
secure a return route,
and then wait until the
infiltration team gets back.
Captain.
I want to avenge
Lambert's death today.
Figured you'd say that...
Yurgis... Assign teams.
Right!
Those with crossbows,
you're on support...
Those with swords, axes,
or defensive artes,
you're on infiltration...
Support team, use the formulas
the captain gave you!
Flynn!
Move!
Yurgis.
Sir?
With me, Flynn.
I thought you disapproved
of this mission.
I always do my duty.
Ready to move?
It's here...! Hurry!
Your fight's over here, monster.
Let's go!
The hard part is
just beginning...
Everyone stay sharp.
Over here, sir.
The aer's flowing from there.
We'll follow it to the source.
What is it?
Watch the edge there, Flynn.
Right.
Gotta go further down.
Looks like that's the
entrance over there.
Hi.
Why are you here?
Not as young as you
used to be, Niren.
I could say the
same to you, geezer.
So... Yuri... What's wrong?
It's lookin' like you're a
little off your game today.
You always butt in like this?
Got a mouth on ya...
We've got our
reasons for coming...
If the town goes under,
then we're outta work...
Plus, I've got some fallen
men who need avenging...
Let's get this over with today.
Captain!
Doesn't hurt anymore...
I'll be fine.
Lose your blastia right now!
What?
If it blows up here,
it'll take us all out.
Yes, sir.
Sure looks like this
is the right way.
Let's go then...
I'm counting on you two.
Niren!
Our swords aren't hurting it.
Flynn!
Yuri...! We need to
cut the red cords!
Yuri!
Yeah!
Let's go!
They keep coming...
You go on ahead.
Thanks, Merzhom.
That's a big boy.
This really hurts.
Oh no!
Someone help...!
Get it off of me!
Yuri... Let's get closer.
I'll toss you up there.
Come on!
Yuri!
So... you okay?
I'm fine.
This is what we've
been looking for.
It's been suckin' up
aer to act as its core.
That's a fancy-lookin'
gadget you found there, Niren.
You okay?
One of my men didn't make it.
I see... I'm sorry.
Who would build
something like this?
We'll find out later.
Supposedly, this will
stop the aer from flowing.
What's that...? It's weird.
No kidding... Very weird.
Hey, it worked!
Chastel, no!
This whole place
is falling apart!
Yuri! We gotta go!
Here, hold this.
What are you stopping for?
Captain...! Look! This core!
Later, Flynn!
Yuri!
Chastel...! Is she okay?
She'll be fine...
She's still breathing.
Sir, you still down there?
Give me your hand!
Take this. We'll hold you.
We're going to get you, sir...
Hold on...! Damn!
It's no use... just go.
Not a chance!
Come on. Give me
your hand, damn it!
'Fraid not...
It's outta commission.
You can get that healed...
Now grab hold!
Yuri.
I still can't reach him...!
Is there something
else we can use?
Yuri!
It's too late for me...
Focus on the people
that you can save.
Take this, too.
Flynn... You look after them.
Become an even greater
Knight than your old man...
and remember your true duty.
No...! Please, Captain...! NO!
Now go.
Later, Niren.
Thank goodness...
You're finally awake.
We're actually still alive.
Yeah... It's over.
Glad you're awake.
So, uh... Where's the captain?
Flynn...! Tell me. Where is he?!
Yuri?
Yeah, he's gone...
but he went out in style.
I know it's a formality,
but it seems silly to
bury an empty casket.
He told me...
that following orders kept him
from protecting his family.
He said that he respected
the decision your father made.
Good grief...
You're still not
finished in here?
He was given specific orders
to stay and hold the fort.
Instead he went off
and got himself killed
on some ridiculous mission.
That fool...
Did he think
disobeying direct orders
would make him some
kind of hero...?
How could you serve
someone so incomp--
Calm down! You know this
guy's not worth it, Yuri!
How dare you come into
his fort and insult him?!
You little brat.
It's time, you two...
Give us a hand.
What kind of brigade is this?!
You said after death,
nothing's left.
But the captain did
leave something behind...
If not for him, the rest us
wouldn't be here. Right?
If you think about it,
your father left a legacy
behind when he died, too...
Always remember that.
One last salute...
For Captain Niren Fedrok
of the Imperial Knights!
Yuri...
It isn't over yet.
We found it inside the ruins.
Only you use that
type of core, sir.
Why did you do it...?!
Were you hoping the town
would be destroyed?
Don't be silly...
We were simply using
those ruins as a test area
for a new type of blastia.
You're creating new blastia?
Correct...
In order to maintain
our way of life,
we must control
aer and blastia...
The only method we
have for obtaining
the necessary crystallized
aer cores is excavation.
But if we could develop
an artificial replacement
for the cores,
it would usher in an era
of greater prosperity,
one free from the
fear of monsters.
But you lost control
of the blastia...
So you decided to destroy it
and take out the brigade
and the town as well.
There was always a
chance it would go awry.
We don't even have control
over normal blastia.
Fortunately for us,
that's how we were able to
bring back that core as proof.
You know, there've been
other experiments
with some measure of success.
Of course...
there were some
casualties then, as well.
Are you saying...
Do accept my condolences.
How awful.
It appears there will be an
unfortunate blastia explosion
here as well.
Feisty one...
You're starting to annoy me.
Damn it.
Flynn... We've got one chance...
Make an opening for me.
I'm on it.
Enough child's play!
It's over!
That's...
His blastia, you bastard.
Captain... It's finished.
Hisca.
You come to see me off?
Yeah... What, are you surprised?
Looks like everybody
else is leaving, too.
The Empire is abandoning
this place now...
so they'll move on.
I noticed the guild guys
didn't waste any time
getting out of town.
I think Merzhom and the
captain were friends...
I'm guessing that's
why he stayed.
Yeah, I know the feeling.
With the captain gone,
I don't think I'm cut out
for the Knights anymore.
I'm sorry... Leaving you
all the clean-up.
I prepared an incident report
and handed it over to
Vice Captain Yurgis...
Garista died in a random
blastia explosion.
We're both covered...
Yurgis suspected Garista too,
once the captain
filled him in...
so he didn't make any objections
to the report I turned in.
You know...
you're tough, Flynn.
They don't make
many guys like you.
Right back at you, Yuri...
Making it in the
world all alone...
Yeah, that's you all right...
As for me, I'm a Knight
through and through.
I'll stay here and do
the best job I can...
Just like the captain ordered.
Oh, that's right...
I guess that you
won't be all alone.
Take good care of it.
See ya around.
Yeah.
See you later...