[RENNER] You spoke with
the Roble Holy Kingdom?
Not quite.
One of their representatives
did come calling, though.
Since they were in
such a dire position,
I thought we might discuss
some countermeasures together.
But you strongly
insisted we should
stand by our foreign policy.
So, what could I say?
You were the one who decided
not to meet with them.
Don't blame me!
You said it yourself,
didn't you?
There's nothing that
our kingdom can do
against a demonic
foe like Jaldabaoth.
[sighs] Let's not point
fingers, dear sister.
The issue is, we keep pushing
all our little problems aside,
and now they've piled up
into quite the mountain.
Since we refused the
Holy Kingdom's request for aid,
they had to turn to
the Sorcerer King instead.
In the end, his forces
defeated Jaldabaoth
and even provided some
generous post-war relief.
They're developing
an air of legitimacy.
If you didn't want them
to deliver the supplies,
then you shouldn't have let
them come through our kingdom.
I did everything in
my power to deter them.
We requested the right to impose
import taxes and charge fees
for the use of our
merchants and warehouses.
The Sorcerer Kingdom
accepted everything
without a hint of resistance.
What could I say?
And now, our nation
is full of their wares,
their wagons, their flags.
Their generosity on display.
Is a bit of charity truly
so threatening to you?
It's not "charity"--
they're plotting something.
Just like with the Empire.
They didn't become
a vassal state
because the Sorcerer
King is nice.
If we became a vassal state,
we might be joining
the winning side.
Have you considered that?
[gasps] Unlike our kingdom,
the Empire has all of its
nobles on a tight leash.
Also, the Sorcerer King
slaughtered us.
Siding with him would
cause a civil war.
Pessimism doesn't
look flattering on you.
[ZANAC]
I know she's just taunting me,
but why do I get the feeling
she wouldn't object
if I bowed down to them?
If only I had Elias's
guidance to rely on.
[RENNER] If you're thinking
about Marquis Raeven,
I doubt we'll be
able to convince him
to return to the capital.
[gasps]
The war with the Empire
crushed his will.
We should consider him
a lost cause, I'm afraid.
That aside, don't you
think it's about time
you ascend to the throne?
[ZANAC]
Huh?
You promised me my own domain,
and I will hold you to that.
Why the delay?
Father's waiting
for the right moment.
He's planning something.
This is a trying
time for us all,
so please be patient for now.
Things will work out.
Soon enough.
[PHILIP]
This was supposed to be easy.
[VIANNEY]
Oh, Baron Montserrat.
[PHILIP]
Baron Delvi. Baron Rokerlen.
Good evening.
[VIANNEY] To our faction's
great leader, Baron Philip!
[GROUP]
Cheers!
My mistake!
It's hardly a drop.
But you seemed quite out
of sorts when we stepped in.
What ails you, friend?
[sighs] I had high hopes
for my faction,
but my all associates have
failed me at every turn!
The commoners are even worse!
I'm the head of the
prestigious Montserrat family!
You'd think they
would listen to me!
Our lands our fertile enough--
If they'd do the work,
we'd be raking it in!
I told them which
cash crops to shift to,
but they still won't do it!
"We don't have the manpower--
too many people died!"
or "Those crops can't grow
in this climate!" Excuses!
Isn't that how it always goes?
When you're ahead of the times,
the world never understands you.
Ignorance is the
enemy of progress
and the bane of a genius
like yourself! Right?
Precisely so.
Ah! It's a joy to speak
with likeminded fellows!
If only someone else would
recognize my sizable talents!
I don't know if I'd say that--
Since you have a backer,
at least one commoner
believes in what you can do!
Yes, Hilma is wonderful.
So true!
And you can drink your fill
whenever you so choose!
She's crafted the perfect
meeting place for your faction,
without asking for
anything in return!
As a proper noble, I intend
to pay her back fully!
Though the whole
kingdom will thank me
once I dismantle our
broken aristocracy!
One's age and rank
isn't everything!
Oh, my! You're such a visionary!
Isn't he?
[YEAG]
Yes. Precisely so.
By the way, I hear you're close
to the Sorcerer Kingdom's
prime minister.
Indeed!
In fact, I'm writing letters
to Lady Albedo constantly!
[gasps] Then you know
of the situation, I assume?
Huh?
It seems the Sorcerer
Kingdom is producing
a huge amount of food,
equivalent to our entire output.
But how?
They're a tiny kingdom and
E-Rantel is their only city!
It's simple.
The undead never tire,
so they're able to cultivate
a massive amount of farmland
in no time at all.
[PHILIP]
How troubling.
It sends a chill down my spine!
But they don't need that food.
It's sent as aid
to the Holy Kingdom.
I've seen it myself,
since convoys from the
Sorcerer Kingdom have been
so brazenly traveling
through my land.
That sounds awful, Lord Vianney.
The thing is, they're storing
that huge supply of food
in warehouses throughout
our kingdom. And the excess
can be sold at rock-bottom
prices any time.
We'll go broke! That's cheating!
[VIANNEY] Lord Philip,
please keep your voice down.
We're struggling enough already!
We can't turn a profit
if someone's undercutting
us that much!
You've gotten right to
the heart of the problem!
I knew you'd understand
if we told you.
[sighs] We need to do something
about this, immediately.
The question is,
how could I make
the Sorcerer Kingdom lower
their production of crops?
[gasps]
No, this is good!
If I can bring down
the hammer of justice
on the Sorcerer Kingdom, not
only will my domain benefit,
I'll be a hero!
It's three birds with
one stone. I can't lose!
[VIANNEY]
Huh?
I think this plan
may interest you.
Let's work together, gentlemen.
[ALBEDO] We're conquering
territories at a good pace,
thanks to the
genius of Lord Ains.
It's hard to keep up.
[ALBEDO] We're lacking
in skilled workers,
but it would look like
a personal failing
if I asked the
Supreme One for help.
[ALBEDO] "Problems encountered
during the transport of aid
to the Holy Kingdom"?
[ALBEDO]
What?
[MOMONGA] I get that we're
trying to show the public
that I have a good
relationship with Momon,
but this oppressive silence
is really ruining the mood.
Not that there's anything
I want to talk to
Pandora's Actor about.
[AINS]
So, uh, Nabe.
Yes?
[AINS]
Just making conversation,
but how is Yuri's
orphanage going?
Have you been?
Not yet, I'm afraid.
[AINS]
Then, should we stop by?
[NARBERAL]
All right.
[chiming]
[ENTOMA]
Lord Ains.
[AINS]
What is it, Entoma?
[ENTOMA] I'm sorry for the
interruption, but Lady Albedo
is requesting your presence
at the Great Tomb of Nazarick
as soon as possible.
[AINS]
Oh?
[ALBEDO] Thank you for heeding
my call so quickly, Lord Ains.
I have gathered all the
floor guardians before you.
[AINS]
Yes. So, I see.
Raise your heads.
[GUARDIANS]
Sir!
[AINS]
It's unusual for you to call
everyone together like this.
Did something troubling occur?
Correct. It was
four days ago.
One of the convoys we deployed
to the Holy Kingdom was robbed.
They were ambushed in Re-Estize.
[AINS]
I see. And the culprit?
It was a noble from Re-Estize.
It was strange.
He had a small army
of commoners with him.
Seems they blocked
our carriages by force.
[AINS] If I remember correctly,
wasn't the convoy
lead by a merchant selected
by the Eight Fingers?
Furthermore, the carriage should
have been flying our flag.
In other words,
Re-Estize decided
to directly attack
the Sorcerer Kingdom.
If not that, then perhaps the
Eight Fingers have betrayed us?
[ALBEDO]
It's not like that.
[AINS]
Hm. What's wrong, Albedo?
[MOMONGA]
Jeez, what's with that look?
It's like when an office worker
screws up something really bad
and has to come
clean to their boss.
I don't remember
any of the nobles
from Re-Estize, though.
Did I piss someone off?
Albedo, don't hold back.
Whatever it is, tell me.
[ALBEDO]
As you wish, My Lord.
If you will recall, we
formulated a plan to take over
the Re-Estize Kingdom by
manipulating a witless noble.
[AINS] Yes, the one you've been
sending letters to, correct?
They aren't personal
letters, I swear!
Wait. Sorry, never mind that.
I'm ashamed to tell you this,
but the robbery
was all his doing.
You're surely thinking
this was a clever ploy,
that the Re-Estize
Kingdom is plotting
something greater against us.
[AINS]
Mm. If that was the case,
then I'm sure you've already
looked into it thoroughly.
Correct.
I have prepared
a witness for you.
This is the one responsible
for managing that noble.
[MOMONGA]
Do I know her?
[HILMA] It's an honor
to see you, Your Majesty.
And in such good health, too!
[AINS] Before we begin, I would
have you state your name.
It's Hilma Cygnaeus,
Your Majesty!
Member of the Eight Fingers!
[MOMONGA]
Okay. Right! That lady!
I-I didn't know anything
about this, I promise!
Why, I would never do anything
that went against your
wishes, Your Majesty!
This was Philip's plan alone!
[AINS]
I see.
Well, I hope you're
telling the truth,
but I will confirm that myself.
[HILMA whimpers]
[AINS]
Dominate.
[AINS] Were you involved
with the robbery
orchestrated by that
noble, in any way?
No, I wasn't.
[AINS] Do you have memory loss
or multiple personalities?
[HILMA]
No, I don't.
[AINS] Hm. And do you have any
intent to operate against us?
[HILMA]
Absolutely not! Never! Never!
[AINS]
A decisive response. Very well.
Even if your actions may
have indirectly triggered
this result, it would be unfair
to blame you for the crime.
I find Hilma Cygnaeus innocent.
But she's still his superior!
His mistakes are hers, too.
A leader must always
take responsibility.
I couldn't believe it!
I never thought he would
do something so insane!
--I warned him many times!
--[ALBEDO] How--
[AINS]
What you said is correct.
A superior should be responsible
for the mistakes of
their subordinates.
However, those words
should be used by a leader
to protect their followers.
It shouldn't be used by another
to force responsibility
on someone beneath them.
Albedo, if she is
responsible for that noble,
who is responsible for her?
Ah, well. That would
be me, My Lord.
[AINS] Correct and by that
measure, I am your master.
Which means this failure is
ultimately my responsibility.
No, not at all, Lord Ains!
I would never dream of blaming
you for this disaster!
[AINS] Cygnaeus, prepare
several new policy changes
and present them to Albedo.
That will be your punishment.
[HILMA]
Yes, My Lord.
[AINS] With that,
the matter is settled.
[NOAH]
Hilma!
How are you?
[OLIN]
I have some fruit liquor here,
if you need to wash
the taste out!
[NOAH] The others are coming
as quick as they can!
[HILMA]
I'm grateful for your concern.
But it's all right.
They didn't do
anything cruel to me.
[GROUP gasps]
Then, what happened?
This time, they took me
before His Majesty.
I spoke with the Sorcerer King.
And he didn't punish you?
[HILMA giggles]
Would you believe it?
He was a kind and
reasonable man.
I went there,
certain that I would die,
but His Majesty was merciful.
He had an air of true wisdom.
I see now that he is worthy of
the throne, above all others!
Hilma, they're simply giving
you the carrot and stick.
[HILMA]
Perhaps you're right.
I've certainly used
that approach myself,
but you could never
understand how it felt!
It was so warm!
It's only because
I've tasted such pain
that the flavor of mercy
is so sweet on these lips.
I felt that I could
trust His Majesty
above anyone else.
More than that,
I wanted to trust him.
Fine, then.
If that's your opinion, we must
show him our unwavering loyalty.
[HILMA]
Indeed! Now, let's get to work!
He's given me a new task!
[AINS]
Surely you didn't call me here
just to pass judgement on her.
Is there something else?
[ALBEDO] Of course,
I'll get straight to it.
That noble is nothing.
but what if someone is using him
for a much larger agenda?
Should we change our approach?
Can we conquer Re-Estize
the same way we planned?
I thought it best
to ask for your opinion
before we went any further.
[AINS]
Mm. I know you and Demiurge
are involved in the operation,
but have you explained the
details to the others yet?
I didn't assume
it was necessary.
[AINS] Then this is a fine
opportunity to tell them.
[MOMONGA]
And me, too, of course.
[ALBEDO]
Understood.
[AINS] I'm interested in hearing
your opinions, everyone.
[GUARDIANS]
Yes, sir.
Operation Carrot and Stick
is quite simple.
We are to conquer the Re-Estize
Kingdom by inciting instability,
and then civil war.
The citizens will come
to beg for our help,
at which point, we will
enter their kingdom
to restore peace,
then bring it under our rule.
Lord Ains came up with the name,
but the suggestion came from
someone within Re-Estize.
To be frank, the idea was
quite clever from the start.
We hardly altered a thing.
But we need that nobleman,
and now he's thrown
the whole plan into disarray.
[MOMONGA]
Wait, he did?
Seems like everything's
working out fine.
Hold on.
[ALBEDO]
What is it, Shalltear?
I'm afraid I'm failing
to see the issue here.
We wanted trouble and the
foolish noble provided it,
without any effort on our part.
[MOMONGA] Thank you!
That's what I'm saying!
He chose the wrong target.
They're supposed to be
unhappy with their own rulers.
I never suspected
they'd be foolish enough
to attack us.
They might have someone
much more clever
than we anticipated
on their side.
If we move carelessly,
we may play
straight into the hands
of an unknown enemy.
[MOMONGA]
Seems like a stretch.
Super geniuses don't just
pop up out of nowhere.
[AINS]
Are you sure that nobleman
didn't do something foolish
on his own accord?
Seems unlikely.
The man is a dunce,
but even that has its limits.
[DEMIURGE]
No, let's think this through.
We can predict the actions
of a logical man,
but not a complete imbecile.
Yet Lord Ains sees the truth
even in a fool's heart.
[GROUP gasps]
Perhaps the simplest
answer is the right one.
Perhaps arrogance and ignorance
warped that man's feeble mind.
No, but how?
No one is that stupid!
Surely not!
If Lord Ains says so,
I trust him.
Humans are not smart at all.
That makes enough sense to me.
[COCYTUS] There is no noble wise
enough to outsmart Lord Ains,
so I don't see why we had
to use one quite so stupid.
Couldn't you find a smart one?
Or are they all this useless?
Some are sensible.
In fact, a number
of capable nobles
have already joined
our side in secret.
But we have decided to gather
all the useless nobles
in a faction together.
A wastebasket we can burn
when the time comes.
[COCYTUS]
Ah, a fine plan.
For now, let's decide
no how we should
respond to this noble.
As I'm sure you are aware,
the convoy they
stole supplies from
bore the flag of
the Sorcerer Kingdom.
How should we punish
such a brazen attack?
Kill them and move on.
[MOMONGA]
Huh?
I don't think there's
any other solution, really.
[MOMONGA]
What?
So, we execute all those
involved in the robbery?
[SHALLTEAR]
That's not enough.
Their masters share the blame,
I say the entire kingdom
should be punished
for their impudence!
[COCYTUS]
I concur, My Lord.
[MOMONGA]
Stop!
That would be
my judgement as well.
But I wonder.
Are you recalling
Lord Ains' words of wisdom?
He told us that it is easy
to rule with violence,
but that gives birth
to more enemies.
And what joy is there
in standing victorious
upon a great pile
of rubble, correct?
[AINS] You remember
my words well, Demiurge.
I'm impressed.
Ooh, I remember them
as well, My Lord!
How could I ever
forget them, Lord Ains?
Uh, me, too!
[AINS]
Yes, yes.
I'm thankful for all of you.
[DEMIURGE] In accordance
with your wishes,
we must refrain from laying
waste to the kingdom.
However, we cannot give them too
light of a punishment, either.
I'm afraid this puts
our current task on hold.
We may have to scrap,
or at least,
substantially rework our plans.
[AINS]
I see.
[MOMONGA]
Well, now I feel guilty.
Seems like a waste to toss
everything out just like that.
[AINS]
Are you certain, Demiurge?
Has our plan truly failed?
[DEMIURGE]
No! What a fool I've been!
Lord Ains is right!
[DEMIURGE]
I see now.
So, this is why you brought
the Empire under your control!
You want to use the
"carrot and stick"
on an international level!
[MOMONGA]
I what?
[gasps]
[GROUP gasps]
[MOMONGA]
Uh...
[AINS]
Precisely.
Thank you for your guidance.
Very well.
Since we've received
permission from Lord Ains,
we'll give Re-Estize
a truly wicked punishment.
[MOMONGA]
What?
The Empire bowed to us quickly,
so they get the carrot,
but the ingrates in
Re-Estize will get the stick.
This message shall
be presented to all.
They will see both your wrath
and your mercy as clear as day.
And suddenly,
every leader in the world
will have to ask themselves,
"which do I want,
the carrot or the stick?"
This is exciting,
Lord Ains, terribly so.
[AINS]
Indeed.
[MOMONGA]
No, no, no!
[ZANAC] Let us begin this
meeting of the royal court.
We have gathered here today
to discuss the letter
we just received from
the Sorcerer Kingdom.
"Our convoy was sending
food to the Holy Kingdom
when it was attacked by a group
of people from Re-Estize."
"We, the Sorcerer Kingdom
consider this action
blatant hostility
and are willing
to declare war if necessary."
They've placed their seal
here, alongside the seals
of the Baharuth Empire,
the Dragon Kingdom,
and the Dwarven Kingdom,
all who support the
contents of this letter.
Next to them is the seal
of the Holy Kingdom,
and the seal of one individual,
known as "Faceless,"
who seems to hold authority
over their temples.
One question. Is it
possible this incident
was caused by the
meddling of a third party,
in order to destroy
our relationship
with the Sorcerer Kingdom?
I can't confirm that there
isn't a larger conspiracy,
but frankly, even if there is,
this falls squarely
on our shoulders.
How far have you looked
into this matter?
The truth is, we have already
confirmed the culprit.
[NOBLES murmur]
Baron Philip Dayton
L'Eyre Montserrat
is the one responsible.
Montserrat?
I've never heard of him.
Whoever he is, I can't imagine
one of our nobles doing
something so obviously suicidal.
This must be a ploy,
orchestrated by the
Sorcerer Kingdom.
[FINANCIAL REPRESENTATIVE]
I agree.
Perhaps he was afflicted
with Charm Person
and made to do it
against his will.
Then we must hurry,
the Sorcerer Kingdom
will want to silence him.
Call him here. He'll
retain his memories,
even if he was mind controlled.
After that, I think we should
we take the man's head.
It will aid our negotiations.
What are you saying, you fool?
[ZANAC] Father. We should
not fight against
the Sorcerer Kingdom,
no matter the circumstances.
Then you would
sacrifice the life
of an innocent noble in an
attempt to appease our enemy?
I ask you, my son,
is that what the future king
of this land should say?
It's not that simple!
Someone who witnessed
the tragedy
of the Katze Plains
should know that.
[gasps]
Even after seeing what
they're capable of,
you still think
it's wise to fight
against the Sorcerer Kingdom?
I'm firmly opposed to it.
Call me cowardly if you like,
but this isn't a battle
we can hope to win.
So, yes.
I would offer up the life of
a nobleman, innocent or not!
I refuse to see our
nation come to ruin!
[gasps]
Your Majesty,
Prince Zanac doesn't
mean to be callous, He simply
wants to protect this kingdom
the same as the rest of us.
Rather than fight, might we
do as the Empire did?
We could submit ourselves
as a vassal state
and settle all this.
Are you out of your mind?
Try showing some dignity!
Minister, this is absurd.
No. I'm afraid
that's the one thing
we simply can't do.
How many lives were lost
protecting this kingdom?
It would be an insult
to their sacrifice
if we gave in so easily.
I do value your opinion,
but I cannot accept this.
[INTERIOR REPRESENTATIVE]
Of course, I understand.
[RAMPOSA III] Zanac. I believe
I might have a solution.
[ZANAC]
Really? You're certain?
[knocking]
[SOLIDER 208A] A herald comes
from the Sorcerer Kingdom!
Prime Minister Albedo will
arrive in the royal capital
any moment now.
[NOBLES gasp]
Very well.
Prepare the throne room and
I will meet with her, myself.
Welcome, Lady Albedo.
It's been some time.
Thank you for seeing me
on short notice, Your Highness.
Now, civilities aside,
what is it that brings
you here today?
Well, just recently,
we were transporting some
relief supplies
through your kingdom.
They were stolen
by a certain noble.
[RAMPOSA III] I just heard
of the matter, myself.
As ruler of this nation,
I would like to apologize
for the inexcusable
actions of my subject.
Furthermore...
...if I were to offer
my head to you,
would that be enough
to settle this matter?