[MARE] This city is bigger
than I thought it'd be.
And I don't see anyone.
There's probably people
hiding everywhere!
And not just soldiers.
I don't think the women
and children fled.
Even if I cause
a big earthquake,
some people might
live through it.
But if I try to burn the city,
people will start
to run and some of
them might get away.
Lady Bukubuku Chagama gave me
all of these powers and I
can't even use them right.
[MARE cries]
[MARE]
No. I can do this!
I'll turn the capital
into rubble
and slaughter every
single person in it!
Burn, smash, kill!
[CLIMB]
It's so quiet.
It's still hard to believe
this is happening.
Princess Renner.
[gasps]
Let's go. There's not much time.
All right.
Did something happen just now?
No, but I remembered a plan
that I need to take care of.
We'll get a little revenge
against the Sorcerer Kingdom.
I'm here, Father!
Renner, what is it?
[RENNER] Just a little idea.
A last-minute plan.
Not for victory, but...
Why do you have those?
Our royal treasures. We've
had these for generations.
It's my duty to
preserve our history.
Though all I can
do now is pass on
these relics to our conqueror.
I will be our final king.
The least I can do is
face the end with dignity.
Now, Climb.
My lord!
[RAMPOSA III]
This is a royal decree.
Take Renner and
escape from here.
There is a secret passage--
take it and it will lead
you outside the city.
That's your last chance
to live. Please, hurry.
There's no need for that.
Don't listen to him.
As I said--
Ignore him. Sorry, father,
but Climb is loyal to me.
He won't follow your
orders over mine.
So I feared.
And yet, loyalty is more
than following orders.
Listen, Climb, in order
to preserve the bloodline
of the Vaiself royal family,
will you take my daughter
and escape this land?
As a reward, I offer you
her hand in marriage.
[CLIMB gasping]
That's very generous.
You flatter me with
such a fine reward.
But I must decline.
Can we get to my plan, please?
Yes, of course, I almost forgot.
I have nothing left
to lose, after all.
Let me take the
royal crown with me.
I'll hide it somewhere
in the capital.
But why?
It's a way to thwart
the Sorcerer King.
We'll tell him we've
hidden our treasures,
the symbols of
this kingdom itself.
And if he reduces
the capital to rubble,
then the trophies of his
conquest will be lost.
That makes sense. As you said,
it won't bring victory,
but it might save a few lives.
Good then.
Climb, I'll leave it to you
to take these and hide them.
Of course, it would be my honor.
Is there someplace in particular
where I should go?
Not to worry.
My brother made a hideout for
us in the warehouse district.
Zanac planned for this?
Indeed. Actually,
it was his idea, as well.
We worked together.
I see. I didn't know he
thought so far ahead.
One last thing.
If that hidden passage
could help Climb,
could you show it to us, please?
Yes.
[CLIMB]
Well, I'll be on my way.
I need you to promise me
something before you go, Climb.
Of course, Princess.
Once you're done, you have to
come back to me safely.
I will!
Don't do anything that would
put you in danger, all right?
That means no fighting.
You have to run.
I'll try. I'll come
back as soon as I can.
[RENNER]
The kingdom is depending on you.
[AURA grunts]
Allow me to confirm
before I draw my sword.
Young man, you work for
the Sorcerer King, correct?
Uh... Here's the thing.
I'm only here to
collect magic items,
so if you can show me
where I can find 'em,
I won't kill you and we can
all be on our merry way.
A bold statement,
but meaningless.
I won't be intimidated
and I'm not here to barter.
If a magic item is desired,
even by a demon,
then it's too dangerous
to hand over.
Wait, that's good! That means
the items are still here!
Okay, one last chance,
if you want to show 'em to me!
Not on my life!
Now, my name is--
I'm on a tight deadline. Why
can't anybody respect that?
Who are they trying to impress?
Well, the mages inside
are probably pushovers.
I bet they'll cave right away.
Oh, you guys can kill 'em now.
[SAMURAI screaming]
[AURA] Hope this stuff
is worth it, Demiurge...
[CLIMB panting]
Gotta get back.
[gasping] What?
[MARE]
Oh! Th-Thank goodness.
Uhm, 'scuse me. I'm afraid
you'll die if you stay here.
Uh, an enemy?
I need to finish my job.
I thought hard and it
makes the most sense
to destroy this place first.
[grunts]
Could you leave, please?
If you don't hurry up, I'm
going to end up killing you
once I start casting spells.
[gasps]
Once you're done, you have
to come back to me safely.
[grunting]
[sighs]
[CLIMB] All those fires...
This is the end!
[CLIMB panting]
Princess Renner!
Anyone here?
In the throne room?
[CLIMB]
I'm coming!
You may enter.
You're the last human
in this palace.
[CLIMB gasps]
No!
You made it.
[gasps]
[CLIMB]
Sorcerer King!
You must show reverence
towards Lord Ains.
Prostrate yourself!
[CLIMB groaning]
This power, you used it on her.
You controlled Princess Renner!
You did this!
You made her kill her father
with her own hands!
[AINS]
Wait, I've seen you before.
You were there
when I had my duel
with Gazef Stronoff,
weren't you?
[AINS]
You may release him.
Sir. You are free to move.
[CLIMB grunts]
All this pain is your fault!
[AINS]
I shall grant you a final honor.
Though I am a king and
you are but a commoner.
I will allow you to fight me.
And... should I win, I will
claim that sword as a prize.
Our kingdom was at peace!
You took that away from us!
You made Princess Renner suffer!
You trampled over the
lives of all her people!
[AINS chuckles]
[yelling]
[RENNER]
Climb!
[screams]
[AINS] If this was a fairy tale,
the strength of
your pure heart would empower
you to vanquish me,
and love would triumph over
my perceived wickedness.
But this is reality.
Unfortunately no such
miracle will happen!
[CLIMB groans]
[AINS]
You will die in short order.
After all, there's no
value in sparing you.
To be frank, you have
no special talent or
power to speak of.
This world is an unfair place.
But that doesn't mean
you should despair.
Inequality exists from
the moment of birth.
There are those who have
talent and those who do not.
Those who are born into wealth
and those born into poverty.
And thus, the fortunate
live a life of comfort,
while the unfortunate are
left to wallow in misery.
No fault of their own.
But there is a truth, even more
absolute than injustice.
Death. For all life
ends in death,
and all are equal
in its embrace.
And that is I. Death itself.
[AINS] There is only one truly
fair thing in this unfair world,
and that is my mercy as
the overlord of death.
I don't care!
[AINS]
Hm...
I am Princess Renner's shield!
[AINS] You have a splendid
fire in your eyes.
[AINS]
Pick it up.
[AINS] It is possible to
harm me with that sword.
Under the right circumstances,
one might even kill me with it.
[RENNER]
Climb!
Tell me this.
Will you kill Princess Renner
after you kill me?
[AINS]
Hm...?
[ALBEDO, DEMIURGE chuckle]
[AINS laughs] What answer
will make you suffer the most?
Or rather, I suspect
that no answer at all
will do the job quite nicely.
I'm not afraid of you!
This is it! Ability Release!
[GAZEF]
Climb. Take this with you.
What is it?
That ring can transcend
human bounds
and push your strength
well past your limits.
[CLIMB yelling]
[CLIMB grunting, yelling]
[AINS]
Clever. That was a fine attack.
[CLIMB screaming]
Climb, no!
[AINS] Is Razor Edge capable
of destroying world items?
Fascinating. I may have
to experiment with that.
But I'm getting ahead of myself.
I have to kill you first.
He's using magic?
On a nobody like me, huh?
[chuckles]
[yelling]
[AINS]
Grasp Heart.
You did well.
[PESTONYA]
If you'll excuse me, woof.
[CLIMB grunting]
[RENNER]
Oh, good. You're awake!
[CLIMB grunting]
Princess... You...
That's right! It's me!
Don't worry, Climb. I'm safe.
[CLIMB gasping]
You noticed my wings.
The Sorcerer King used his
powers to change me into this.
I'm afraid that I'm no longer
human. I'm a demon.
[CLIMB gasping]
I know it's shameful of me.
So many people died
and I'm here like this.
[grunting]
You must be confused.
You lost to the Sorcerer King
and you're wondering why
you're still alive, right?
[grunts]
I'll tell you, of course.
But first, I fear I have a
selfish request to ask of you.
As I said, I've turned
into a demon.
Unlike a human,
I'll live for eternity.
I'll be left all alone.
Please, Climb. Stay with me.
Become a demon like I did.
[grunts]
I know you'd never leave me.
Now, I said I'll tell
you why you're alive.
The truth is,
you died back there,
but you were resurrected
by the will of
the Sorcerer King.
He did it as a personal favor
because I pledged
my allegiance to him.
[gasping]
Can you do that?
Can you pledge
allegiance to him, too,
so we can be together?
[grunting]
Y-Yes.
[RENNER] I'm certain
that the Sorcerer King
will test your loyalty
in some way.
Whatever it is,
I'm afraid it will be
terribly painful for you.
I know that's the only way,
but it still hurts my
heart to think of it.
Don't worry. I'll make
it through for you.
I'm so glad to have you.
But let's not worry about
these things right now.
We have plenty of time.
All you need to do now is rest.
[gasps] Forgive my rudeness,
Lady Albedo!
And I apologize. I should
have thanked you sooner.
It's gone so quickly.
I forgot my manners.
Thank you for preparing the
poison and playing along
with my charade in
the throne room.
The Sorcerer King has
been most generous
in his support of my proposals.
I'm undeserving of such mercy.
[laughs] It's adorable, but you
don't need to be nervous.
The plan to destroy the kingdom
was almost entirely yours,
after all, and you
played your part well.
We know what you're capable of.
You've proven yourself plenty.
Just keep up the good work,
and I'm sure you'll make
a fine addition
as my subordinate.
But of course. I'll do my best.
Lord Ains must think
you have great potential,
seeing how much
trouble he went to.
You're starting out
with a debt to pay.
[gasping]
[ALBEDO] But that's all right.
In fact... I'll reward you
for your next thousand
years of work in advance.
This is another Seed of the
Fallen, for your little puppy.
Thank you for your faith.
And please express my gratitude
to His Majesty as well.
I'll work hard to repay him.
In fact, I'll work hard enough
to repay him several times over.
Heh. On that note, I have
some lingering matters
to attend to,
if you'll excuse me.
[sighs]
Seems I'll be able to clear
that final hurdle after all.
Only one thing defied
my calculations.
I never thought His Majesty
would make a personal appearance
just to play such a
ridiculous role. Oh well!
It didn't take long at all
to make my dream come true.
And all I had to do was
sell out one measly kingdom
to achieve it.
I'm truly blessed.
Oh, Climb. I hope you're ready
for an eternity of
happiness by my side!
We should celebrate,
shouldn't we?
If I were to share my
first time with you,
how would you like that?
Oh, but it's too early.
I have to build your
anticipation a bit, after all.
[RENNER laughing]
[DEMIURGE]
Lord Ains.
I'd like to make a request--
if you'll indulge me.
After reading over
Sebas' findings,
there is one place
I would like to see.
Could I impose on you, Lord?
[AINS]
I don't mind.
You are acting for the benefit
of Nazarick, aren't you?
Go ahead. Enjoy.
I plan to, Lord.
[RENNER] Is that you, Climb?
Please, come in.
I'm sorry for being gone
so long, Princess.
I was terribly worried.
Uh?
I couldn't help but fear
the worst for you,
[RAEVEN] I hear you plan to go
up against Eight Fingers.
Where will you be attacking?
[RENNER]
Seven locations.
Also, sister, I have an
important question to ask you.
You're aware that our
beloved older brother
is also taking money from
Eight Fingers, right?
[gasps] Not Brother Barbo.
This could be our
opportunity to depose him!
We should definitely
consider including
his drug division stronghold
in your plan of attack.
Taking out eight targets is
obviously better than seven.
[DEMIURGE]
What I'm about to tell you
is a matter of great importance.
Entoma?
[ENTOMA]
Acknowledged.
Killing this person
is strictly forbidden.
Understood, Shalltear?
Oh, ha-ha! Poke fun
at the vampire,
why dontcha? Jerk.
[DEMIURGE]
Hm? What is it, Shadow Demon?
Excellent. It appears
we now have one more
Eight Fingers base
to attack tonight.
Mare. You and Entoma will
focus on the new location.
[SHALLTEAR]
Insolent ant!
I refuse to let a measly human
escape from me unharmed.
Time Accelerator!
[SHALLTEAR]
Is that...?
[CLIMB] Princess Renner has
requested that I go into battle
without changing my armor.
[PHILIP]
Hey, is anyone there?
You're s'posed to serve me.
Ingrates.
[ALBEDO]
Oh, good. Awake at last.
[gasps] What are you doing here?
I set up a barrier to keep
you isolated from the war.
But it was so peaceful
and quiet in here,
I feared you might
sleep forever.
Well! I'm honored you
made the trip to see me!
[gasps]
You're here to save me because
you know what I'm worth!
They thought they could
use me as a scapegoat!
But you... you
understand that I was
a victim and their
envy is at fault!
I never lost faith!
I knew you were wise!
All I've ever done was work hard
to make this kingdom
a better place!
Ha! I admit you've
rendered me speechless.
At this point, I can
only be impressed.
Oh, before I forget,
I brought you a little gift.
How considerate of you!
[PHILIP yelping]
[ALBEDO]
You sullied my good name.
I was kind enough to
associate with you,
and this is how you act?
[PHILIP whimpering]
Your father begged and
begged me before he died.
Not for mercy, mind you.
He wanted to make
sure you suffered
as much as his
people did and more.
I have every intent to
honor his dying wish.
[PHILIP screaming]
[RAEVEN]
Your Majesty, we've come from
our domains to greet
you, as decreed.
[AINS] Marquis Raeven,
was it? A pleasure.
[RAEVEN grunts]
[AINS] Perhaps I should
commend you for your efforts,
but I do detest idle chatter.
Instead of wasting
our time any further,
I suggest we end this quickly.
I trust no one has
any objections?
[RAEVEN]
No, My Lord.
[AINS] The Sorcerer Kingdom's
army will continue its assault.
We will destroy the
remaining noble fiefs,
then return home.
In the meantime,
continue governing
your own domains as usual.
We may relocate some
of you in the future,
but there are no such
plans at the moment.
Is all of that correct, Albedo?
Indeed. Just as you
say, Lord Ains.
[AINS]
There you have it.
Govern as you wish
until told otherwise.
[RAEVEN]
Thank you.
[AINS] As you can see,
the Kingdom has fallen.
Nothing remains of the capital.
With that in mind, I'd like
to ask you something.
Of course. As you wish.
[AINS] Do you think
rulers will understand
the futility of defying me?
In lands far and wide?
[RAEVEN]
Yes, Your Majesty.
This rubble will
serve as a monument.
And tales of what befell
the people here
will travel the lands for
countless ages to come.
[AINS] I see. Then it was
well worth the effort.
I am thoroughly satisfied
with this result.