[PANDORA'S ACTOR]
So then I bowed down and said,
"Please, I beg of you!
Just a moment of your time!"
And it worked splendidly.
He stopped dead in his tracks.
[ALBEDO]
May I interject?
[PANDORA'S ACTOR]
What is it?
You were posing as
Lord Ains--the Sorcerer King
and absolute ruler of
the Tomb of Nazarick.
And yet you dropped
to your hands and knees.
Is that appropriate?
[PANDORA'S ACTOR]
Oh, you're right.
I don't suppose the real Lord
Ains would ever do such a thing.
[AINS] No, I think that
was a fine choice.
If that's all it takes to make
an enemy drop their guard,
then feel free to debase
yourself all you like.
My dignity is not so flimsy
as to be shaken by such a thing.
In addition to taking
him off guard,
I'm certain that it led him
to underestimate me.
You've poisoned his
mind quite skillfully.
[PANDORA'S ACTOR]
Thank you.
[AINS] But we still don't
have enough information.
Some of his powers are still
a bit of a mystery to me.
[PANDORA'S ACTOR]
Like the barrier, you mean?
[AINS] Since Albedo was carrying
Ginnungagap and she was
the only one who could
break through the barrier,
we can assume it was
created using a world item.
It likely functions the same as
the world item I gave to Aura--
Depiction of Nature and Society.
[PANDORA'S ACTOR]
I'm not so certain, My Lord.
I noticed something peculiar.
When he spoke the words
"World Isolation Barrier,"
his HP dropped. Perhaps
it was actually a skill?
[AINS]
Yes. Although some world items
have an activation cost,
I've never heard of one
that takes your HP.
And you said that
his HP dropped
when he used other skills
as well, is that correct?
[PANDORA'S ACTOR] Yes, even
for things like teleportation.
His HP would drop
upon activation.
[AINS] One world item
with multiple functions?
Such things do exist,
like my orb here.
But the ability to strengthen
weapons and armor,
teleport, and create barriers?
Those abilities are far too
different from one another.
As things stand,
we cannot say for certain
that his skills are
the work of a world item.
It seems we need to lose
another battle with this
Riku fellow if we
want to find out.
[BOTH gasp]
[AINS] Naturally,
I don't like losing, either,
but we must know everything
possible about our opponent.
That will ensure
an absolute victory.
[ALBEDO, PANDORA'S ACTOR]
Yes, sir!
[MOMONGA] I've confirmed that
NPCs can be resurrected,
and that goes for people
from this world, too.
But if I die, who knows?
Not really something I can test.
Well, actually, thinking
about the history here.
The Six Great Gods
and the Eight Greed Kings
were probably players like me.
Without exception, all of their
stories end with their deaths.
That means my odds aren't good.
I have to keep that in mind
with every decision
that I make going forward.
Anything that's lost
can be regained,
as long as I'm still alive.
Better to suffer a strategic
loss and live to tell the tale.
[AINS] Well, then,
Cocytus and the others
should be attacking the
royal capital about now.
I'll head there, as well.
I need to close the curtain
on this tale personally.
[ALBEDO] It's such a
trivial matter, My Lord.
Are you certain it's
worthy of your attention,
when I could take
care of it for you?
[AINS laughs]
When I'm playing the villain,
I have standards to uphold.
Though I'm not quite as
extravagant about it as Ulbert.
Oh, is that why?
Well, fair enough then.
[AINS] Yes, that is
exactly why, Albedo.
It's good that you understand.
[CARETAKER 412A] I know this
is a strange time to say this.
But the children look
forward to your visits
more than anything else.
They always love your stew.
It's been difficult to get some
ingredients because of the war,
but with your help today,
the children will finally
be able to eat their fill.
Well, I hope you're able to have
a bit of stew yourselves.
You've been saving food
for the children,
so I'm sure you haven't
been eating properly.
[CARETAKER 412B sobs]
You're so kind, princess.
Pathetic, isn't it?
[gasps]
Can you believe it?
Our kingdom's on
the brink of ruin,
and feeding orphans
is all I can do.
It's only a matter of time
before the Sorcerer
Kingdom arrives.
Then, all of the people here
in the capital will die.
Please don't say that.
No matter what happens next,
the children are
happy right now.
That wouldn't be
the case without you.
[gasps]
[laughs] I...
I'm sorry, I said too much.
That was insolent of me.
[giggles]
I'm sure you must be busy,
so thank you for
meeting with me.
I apologize for
making you wait.
[LAKYUS]
That's perfectly fine.
You probably have plenty
to take care of, yourself.
Oh. I don't need tea.
I'm afraid we can't stay long.
[EVILEYE]
Come on, Lakyus.
How long could it take
to drink one cup of tea?
Were all of you
looking forward to it?
[EVILEYE] The princess extends
us such a kind offer
in this trying time and you turn
it down without a thought?
How cold of you.
Hey, muscle-head.
[EVILEYE] Don't ignore me.
Who do you think I'm talking to?
Miss "I'd sink in the
water like a rock."
[EVILEYE sighs]
Hey, Gagaran.
Yes? What is it?
[EVILEYE] Wouldn't you like
to have a spot of tea?
More than just a spot.
I could chug the stuff
by the gallon.
My poor throat has
never been so parched.
[EVILEYE]
So there you have it, Boss.
Tea for everyone.
With your permission.
If it means that much to you.
But you'll be drinking, as well?
[TIA] We'll pour the
cups. Don't worry.
Uh--
You can have a nice chat
with the princess
in the meantime, okay?
Though fair warning,
I like my tea extremely bitter.
That's not necessary.
There's some in the pot.
Oops, there's not enough.
Oh, no. That won't do at all!
Especially since we have
someone who could, quote:
"chug the stuff
by the gallon."
People will start to think
the princess can't even
offer tea to her
distinguished guests!
Stop it, you're being rude!
[RENNER]
Lakyus.
This is probably the last time
we'll see each other.
Your friends are only trying
to buy us some time.
[gasps]
[TINA]
Hey, Brain.
[TIA] Show us where
we can boil more water.
All right. Straight ahead.
So should I leave
the room, as well?
[EVILEYE]
Don't worry about it.
You're fine. They didn't
leave with Brain
just to give the
princess privacy.
Let's relax.
Your friends were
so considerate.
Fair enough. There's no harm.
We can chat until the
tea gets here at least.
I agree!
I don't sense anyone nearby.
Guess they've all run away.
Your tea.
[LAKYUS]
Where are Sir Unglaus and Tina?
[TIA]
Looking for dessert.
[LAKYUS]
You're serious?
Here, slave-driver.
You're about to taste the first
tea that I've ever made.
Quite the honor, right?
Such a strong aroma.
I can't wait.
Drink it. In one gulp.
You should find it
quite refreshing,
since you're a demon.
I'll humor you this time,
but only because
it's your first try.
Delicious?
I think that might be a stretch.
It's very bitter.
[gasps]
[TIA]
All right. One more!
[screams]
Princess, stay behind me!
What's going on here?
[EVILEYE]
You move and I cast a spell.
Don't bother.
You're not our target.
Besides, this will
all be over soon.
[LAKYUS groans]
But why?
I've been watching you
for a long time.
Figuring out what it would
take to bring you down.
It's your turn, Evileye.
[EVILEYE]
Right. Resist Weakening.
Nope. Blocked it.
Why don't you justgive up?
[EVILEYE]
Resist Weakening.
Now it worked.
Charm Person.
Good. Got her.
All right!
[EVILEYE] Lakyus, be a good girl
and heal your wounds.
Right. As you wish.
Uh--
[RENNER] Mind control
is truly frightening.
[EVILEYE] Look at you!
Not shaken up one bit!
You may act girly, but I
always knew you were tough.
I've never thought of
myself that way at all.
I just had faith. Or rather,
I knew you wouldn't
do something like this
without a reason.
On that note.
Can you tell me why you poisoned
and mind-controlled your friend?
[EVILEYE]
It's nothing complicated.
This might sound callous,
but the truth is,
we care more about Lakyus than
we care about the kingdom.
Our fiendish boss
was the only one
who wanted to protect
the royal capital.
The rest of our group was
secretly against that plan.
But there was no point
in arguing with her about it.
She'd stay behind on her own
and tell us that we should go.
The only solution we thought
of was to catch her off-guard
and take her out of
the capital by force,
but I'm sorry you
had to see this.
[EVILEYE] We had to make sure
she didn't have her magic items,
then we used five
different poisons
and cast weakening spells.
Even then, getting Charm Person
to work was a gamble.
[EVILEYE]
That's that!
As soon as Tina comes back,
we'll teleport
out of the capital.
Do you two want to come with us?
Could we?
Before I can answer,
I have to know,
where are you planning
to run off to?
[EVILEYE] Tough call.
Somewhere southeast?
There's a kingdom there that
fell to ruin a long time ago.
In short, it's someplace far,
far away that you've
never heard of.
Is that so?
Thank you for the offer. But no.
I believe I'll stay here.
[EVILEYE]
Very well.
[knocking]
[TINA] Good news!
We found some dessert.
It took us forever, because she
couldn't pick out just one.
Huh? What happened?
You wanna explain
all the blood?
Everything's fine.
It's nothing to
concern yourself with.
All right, then.
I guess I'll just
leave it at that.
[EVILEYE]
Here's a question, Brain.
Do you want to escape with us?
Is Princess Renner
going as well?
I see. In that case, I'll pass.
That works out just fine for me.
I'm tired of running away.
[EVILEYE]
Of course.
How did I know that's
what you'd say?
Well, so long, then.
Teleportation.
Uh, Princess.
[BRAIN]
All right, it's time.
This is yours. I'll be
heading out on my own.
To what end?
I'll hunt down the Sorcerer King
and challenge him to a duel.
Though I admit, that's
probably a tall order,
since he's got a whole army
out there protecting him.
[CLIMB]
Wait a second!
This sword was
left in your care!
That was Sir Stronoff's
wish before he was killed!
Too bad, then.
I already told you, didn't I?
I have no intentions
of respecting his wishes.
I'm sorry, but could you return
that sword to the king for me?
[RENNER]
As you wish.
But, Princess!
It's fine.
We should respect
Sir Brain's decision.
You always impress, Princess.
You're a lady worth serving.
Not that I know
much about ladies,
if I'm being totally honest.
We've had some
good times, Princess.
And Climb.
I still remember when I met
you and Lord Sebas.
It brought me back to life.
This is probably our farewell,
but hey, I've got no regrets.
Why did everything
have to fall apart?
No, it was destroyed
by the Sorcerer King!
[RENNER]
Climb. Let's go.
I still have to fulfill
my royal duty.
That sword is our
kingdom's treasure.
I'd like to deliver
it to my father
while that's still possible.
Yes. Of course.
But before we get to that.
Indulge me.
Just for a moment, let me
hold the sword, myself.
Huh? Sure. Be careful.
My goodness, it's quite heavy.
I suppose it doesn't
suit me much.
Actually, I'm not sure
I would say that, Princess.
In fact, you'd probably
surpass me easily
with a bit of training.
You don't always
have to flatter me.
Either way, I don't think
I'll have the chance
to wield a sword ever again.
Uh...
All right.
I need to make
a few preparations.
Then we'll see Father.
[AURA] Hey, guys!
Nobody try to stop me, 'kay?
Nailed it!
I'll only say this
one more time.
Don't try to stop me.
I'm real busy.
Hm... That's there so, this way?
Hey! Don't ignore me!
Come on, guys.
I'm not the only enemy here.
Can you afford to get distracted
at a time like this?
My friends are coming!
[SOLDIERS gasp, yelp]
Don't bother with them.
The troops aren't
my responsibility.
Okay. First stop is
the magician's guild.
Oooh! I found it!
[screams]
[SOLDIERS groan]
[AURA sighs]
It's okay.
Iri just got a
little too excited.
But I'm not mad.
You don't have to bully him.
You ready?
Who wants to help me destroy
a couple of buildings?
But this is precision work.
Iri's too big.
Don't be sad.
I have a special mission
just for you!
Go stomp around the city walls.
And squish everyone you
see under your feet!
Okay, the rest
of you, follow me.
[AURA giggles]
[BRAIN]
Let's see.
If I were the Sorcerer King,
then where would I be?
Maybe I should hide in
a building and wait for him.
Seems they haven't
started the attack yet.
The civilians either couldn't
escape or they were too scared.
Don't they realize they're
just waiting to die?
If they all came out to fight at
once, it'd be a hell of a show.
Would things have been
different if he was here,
instead of me?
Well, no point in
wondering that now.
It feels cold.
I'll try it. Why not?
Just waltzed right up.
No backing down now.
[BRAIN] Actually,
I'm surprised he stopped.
I'm nothing more than an ant
in his path, after all.
And he'll be crushing plenty of
ants today, seeing as there's
hardly anyone willing or able
to defend the capital.
En garde! I am Brain Unglaus!
[COCYTUS]
And I am Cocytus.
A servant of the Supreme Being,
the Sorcerer King,
Ains Ooal Gown.
Well met, swordsman.
[gasps]
Thank you for this.
[COCYTUS]
No need.
God Slaying Emperor Blade.
Heh.
"Seek life when facing
death," he said.
Good advice.
I can't survive a
single strike of his.
My only hope is to move so fast
that I take out his arms
before he attacks.
This is it!
Time for Ability Boost!
[BRAIN]
And Greater Ability Boost!
True Nail Clipper!
[BRAIN groans]
[COCYTUS] I wasn't told that
there were any men of merit
left in this land.
He might have become a
great asset had he joined us,
and yet, I cut him down.
I must respect the
resolve of a warrior
the moment he draws his sword.
I am certain that Lord Warrior
Takemikazuchi would accept
my decision, if he were here.
[COCYTUS]
I will take this as a trophy.
Preserve his body in ice.
We shall continue our advance.
[COCYTUS]
Hm.