[AINS]
How shall I forge this kingdom?
[MOMONGA]
What did Ulbert used to say?
Something about an
iron-fisted dictatorship
being the way to go?
That certainly is
the kind of leadership
Albedo and Demiurge favor,
and if nothing else,
they're very good at their jobs.
I don't share their passion
for world domination,
but I don't reject
the idea, either.
I've let them do as they wished.
[FITH whimpers]
[MOMONGA] But now
I want something more,
something for myself.
I want this kingdom to be
a haven for all races,
where all of them
are treated equally.
Then, even if I can't
see my friends again,
I can at least relive our
glory days, or that's the idea.
--[AINS sighs]
--[FITH yelps]
[MOMONGA] But if I tell Albedo
and the others my feelings,
it might upset
their current plans.
They might not even agree.
Maybe I should do things
on my own for now.
[FITH]
Please forgive me, My Lord!
[AINS]
Hm?
[FITH]
To think that you would let out
such a deep sigh on my watch!
I don't know how
I've failed you,
but such a crime can only
be punishable by death!
[AINS]
What? No! Why?
[RENNER] And so, the brave
knight defeated the dragon
and saved the princess from
its villainous clutches.
Then,
they lived happily ever after.
[GIRL 402A]
Oh, yay!
[GIRL 402B]
She deserved a happy ending!
--[BOY 402A] That was fun!
--[RENNER] Yes, I agree.
[EVILEYE]
Hey, the brat's here for you.
I tried to wait till
the story was done.
It's time to return
to the royal palace.
You gotta go
already, Princess?
Don't worry, I'll be back soon
and we'll cook
something delicious!
[CHILDREN chattering]
[EVILEYE]
That was quite an impressive
orphanage you
started. Expensive?
My brother understood the
necessity and payed for it
as soon as I asked.
The Sorcerer King
caused many deaths
and that means many children
were left without parents.
[EVILEYE] I'm afraid I don't see
the value in this investment.
The weak are destined to perish.
Then what good is my power?
It is the duty of the strong
to protect the weak.
We can't leave them to die!
This isn't a burden at all--
those children are my treasures.
Uh--
I will ensure that
they don't wander
from the path of righteousness.
The future of the
kingdom is at stake.
That's quite the
wise perspective.
[EVILEYE] Not everyone can
be strong, like Rigrit said.
He told me the same thing.
Guess it must be
his catchphrase.
[EVILEYE]
Maybe.
Anyway, children without parents
do have a higher tendency
to get involved in crime.
We need to nurture
the children's talents,
so they become an
asset to the kingdom.
Then other nobles will
start to copy the idea.
[EVILEYE]
That's pretty clever.
No one does charity without
expecting something in return.
[TINA] You only think that
'cause your heart is twisted.
[EVILEYE] Oh, come on,
like you're any different!
My heart is pure.
You're the only
tainted one here.
[EVILEYE sighs]
To be honest, the orphanage
idea came from Brain.
He wants to find children that
have a talent for swordsmanship,
but I'm looking for more.
You were there.
Maybe you can help!
Did you sense anything?
Did any of the orphans you saw
seem to have a hidden talent?
I don't know,
I was standing outside.
Did you catch anything?
[EVILEYE] I can't tell if
a kid has magical potential
just by looking at them.
That's a pity.
Do the two of you have hidden
talents? Just out of curiosity.
It's a secret.
[EVILEYE] I don't even
know how to answer that.
Why do you care?
Perhaps because most people
I know are so untalented.
[EVILEYE]
Not all of them.
You do have a talent!
Tell me!
Have you known since
you were young?
I know you think it's silly,
but please indulge me!
[EVILEYE sighs] I like
to keep this a secret, okay?
So, I'll whisper it to you.
Thank you!
[EVILEYE] A talent is an
adventurer's trump card.
Of course.
[EVILEYE] So, you really think
I'm gonna tell you just for fun?
[CLIMB yelps]
That was terribly cruel!
My ears are ringing!
[CLIMB]
Poor princess!
Lady Evileye, please
show her some mercy.
[EVILEYE]
Don't blame me!
She's like that because
you coddle her so much!
Ah--! I do no such thing!
[RENNER]
I agree!
But if you're going
to get accused of it,
you might as well
coddle me more!
It's good you brought up
this issue, Evil Eye.
[EVILEYE]
You really twisted that around.
I have some suggestions
to get us started.
For example, we can
take naps together
like when we were children!
[CLIMB]
Princess, no.
[EVILEYE sighs]
Fine, we can talk about talents!
I keep mine a secret, but let's
just say it's really dangerous.
Strong enough to level
an entire city,
like if Lakyus's sword
went on a rampage.
It's a last resort.
Her sword is that
strong? Really?
[EVILEYE]
According to her, at least.
She says she has to
channel her own power
just to keep it
at bay sometimes.
Our boss keeps that to herself
'cause she doesn't
want to worry you.
So, pretend you
never heard this.
--Of course, you have my word.
--[CLIMB] Um, Princess Renner?
[RENNER]
Oh my! How careless!
[CLIMB] Speaking of which,
where's Lady Aindra right now?
I haven't seen her in a while.
She's helping train
Gagaran and Tia.
[EVILEYE] They were revived
after Jaldabaoth killed them,
but they lost a lot of
life force in the process.
They're engaging
in intensive training
to strengthen themselves.
They have to get back
to their former power.
If that demon attacked now,
we wouldn't be able
to buy enough time.
Buy time for what?
Oh, you're thinking your hero
will come to the rescue, huh?
[EVILEYE]
That's right!
Lord Momon will
save the day for sure!
Haven't you heard?
He's so strong, he can swing
a giant sword like a twig!
He's the best warrior
on the continent,
maybe in the whole world!
We wouldn't have to worry about
Jaldabaoth with him around,
or the Sorcerer King!
He can beat anyone!
Uh--
You just remembered, huh?
He can't beat the Sorcerer King
'cause he works for him.
[EVILEYE]
Why, Lord Momon?
What are you thinking?
You reminded me.
I have a question.
One-on-one.
How well do you think you'd do
against the Sorcerer King?
[EVILEYE] Not well at all, if
the rumors about him are true.
I would be dead in an instant.
I'm pretty sure Lord Momon
is the only person
who might be able
to stand up to him.
So, the Sorcerer King
recruited the only man
capable of fighting against him.
Now we have two
invincible enemies.
[MILITARY AFFAIRS]
The adventurers are continuing
their search for Prince Barbro,
but they haven't found
so much as a hint
of his whereabouts.
It's been quite some time.
There's little hope
that he's still alive.
Keep searching for him
all the same.
It shall be done, Prince.
Really now, Brother, must you
be a nuisance to the very end?
There's one more thing.
Go ahead.
[MILITARY AFFAIRS]
How is Marquis Raeven?
I haven't heard a
single word from him.
He's retreated to his private
territory and shut himself in.
His encounter with
those monsters
must've given him
quite the fright.
[knocking]
What is it?
[MAID 402A]
Princess Renner has returned.
[ZANAC] I was hoping that I
could rely on Marquis Raeven's
expert guidance, but I fear
he may never return.
Well, that's a problem
for another day.
Right now, as next
in line for the throne,
I need to decide how to deal
with the Sorcerer Kingdom.
[gasps]
[ZANAC]
I should send them a tribute,
if only to keep them at bay.
My concern is that our nobles
and the neighboring
countries may see it
as a sign of submission.
They're just looking
for someone to blame.
Thank you for coming
out to meet me.
I hope you're well.
All things considered, I'm fine.
Shall we take a little walk?
I'd be delighted.
A representative of the Sorcerer
Kingdom will arrive soon.
If you were planning
to offer them a tribute,
now is your chance.
I would double the
amount, and give it
to their representative
in honor of their visit.
Even the nobles would struggle
to find fault in that.
[SOLDIER 402A]
My prince, we have been notified
that a delegation from the
Sorcerer Kingdom has arrived.
Then I shall greet them.
[SOLDIER 402A]
Understood.
If I become king,
I'll give you domain
in some remote area,
far away from all of this.
You can live out
your days in peace.
That's very kind of you.
I'm grateful.
Though frankly, it's not a
very appealing suggestion,
and it's far too late
for that now.
[BRAIN]
Six Fold Flash of Light!
Impressive work.
[VESTURE]
You've changed. I can tell.
You think so?
[VESTURE] You had such
a sour look on your face
when you lost in
the last tournament.
[BRAIN] I thought I could stand
amongst the strong back then.
You might say I learned
a valuable lesson.
One must "seek life
when facing death."
You cannot defeat a monster
without betting it all.
You must offer your life for
even a small chance of victory.
My measly life
would be a bargain
for a victory against him.
[VESTURE] Is the Sorcerer King
truly that powerful?
He is. For one, he defeated
your prize student
Gazef in the blink of an eye.
I wouldn't call him my student.
I just showed him
a trick or two.
A "trick," huh?
Funny you say that,
since I heard you taught him
your strongest Martial Art.
Vesture Kloff Di Laufen's
famous technique.
The legacy of an
adamantite adventurer.
And while we're
talking about legacy.
I'm looking for someone to
take up Gazef's former job,
but for a commoner with
no connections, it's not easy.
You could be chief
warrior yourself.
[BRAIN]
I'm not fit for it.
That's why I'm looking
to the next generation.
There are some kids
with good potential,
but I'll have to wait a while
for them to grow up.
It seems that you're quite
committed to this endeavor.
This land needs strong warriors,
and the more the better.
Our enemy is the
Sorcerer King, after all.
[ZANAC] I assume this weather
is the work of their magic.
Here they come.
[gasps]
[DEATH CAVALIER] Apologies for
speaking to you from my mount!
We are the delegation
from the Sorcerer Kingdom.
I am the second prince
of the Reestize Kingdom.
Zanac Valleon Igana
Ryle Vaiself.
His Majesty welcomes you.
Please allow me to guide your
party to the royal palace.
[DEATH CAVALIER]
Very well.
Pardon the lack of introduction.
We have no individual names.
You may address me by
my race: "Death Cavalier."
As you wish, then, Sir Cavalier.
But before we proceed,
might I be allowed
to greet the leader of
your honored delegation?
[DEATH CAVALIER]
I shall fetch them.
Brace yourselves, everyone.
And don't do anything
that could offend them.
[SOLDIERS]
Sir!
[DEATH CAVALIER]
Pardon the wait.
Allow me to introduce the
leader of our delegation.
She is the closest aide to the
Sorcerer King, Ains Ooal Gown.
Lady Albedo.
[PHILIP] Look at you,
with your fancy clothes.
You probably think
I'm not worth a damn.
I have my father
to thank for that.
He's a failure as a noble.
But that's all right.
Once I'm in charge,
I'll turn this family around.
I'll show all these
bumbling lords and ladies
what a real noble looks like.
[OFFICER 402A] Everyone,
your attention, please!
I would like to introduce
the diplomatic envoy
of the Sorcerer Kingdom,
Lady Albedo!
[gasps]
[PHILIP]
She's gorgeous.
This is it.
I can't let this
chance go to waste.
[PHILIP chuckles]
I'm so lucky!
No, it's more than that.
I'm a genius!
I'll show you how it's done.
If you wanna make
a change in this world,
you've got to bet it all!
Lady Albedo.
[PHILIP] My name's Philip
Dayton L'Eyre Montserrat.
I am the sole heir of
the Montserrat Barony.
Call me Philip.
It's such an honor to meet you.
[PHILIP'S FATHER] What are
you thinking, you fool?
Do you know how many
strings I had to pull
just to get you
invited to that party?
This was a chance to have
you recognized as my heir!
You need to be strengthening
your relationship
with the other nobles,
not inviting some monster
from the Sorcerer
Kingdom to a ball!
Where are you going to hold it?
Certainly not here!
But it's too late
to back out now.
Calm down, Father. This'll
be an excellent opportunity,
just trust me.
You realize our
situation, right?
Where's our domain located?
We're between the capital
and the Sorcerer Kingdom!
So that means we
need to strengthen
our relationship with them.
That would be treason!
Why would you join forces
with the Sorcerer Kingdom
when they killed
your own brother?
If you put it that way,
they did me a favor,
seeing as I'm the sole heir
to the domain now.
How could you say that?
You've gone mad!
This is all for our sake!
To protect our domain
and its people!
What happens when the Sorcerer
Kingdom decides to invade?
It's better to be on
the winner's side, I say!
[PHILIP'S FATHER]
And leave the others to die?
I was the first to
approach the envoy.
What happens to everyone
else is their problem.
[PHILIP'S FATHER] Won't that
antagonize our neighbors?
What if they turn on us?
Even if they're angry, it's not
like they would attack us.
Their men died
in the war too, y'know.
As you said, many died.
Production will suffer for it.
The domains have to
work together closely
to share their resources. But
we only have a single village,
with little to offer them.
We still need their support!
If that's the case,
the Sorcerer Kingdom
can provide so much more!
We're a village
in an enemy nation.
Would you aid us if you
were the Sorcerer Kingdom?
It shows character, of course!
Their new king needs
to improve his public image
and that would be
an easy way, right?
[PHILIP'S FATHER]
That's the only reason?
Well, it's enough reason for me!
Try to be more
open-minded, father.
As long as we use
our brains a bit,
the Sorcerer King is
nothing to be afraid of.
He's just another tool
to help forge my future--
or, the future of
our family, I mean.
If that's how you feel, I have
nothing left to say to you.
Actually, sir, there's
one more problem.
We never settled the
issue with the ball.
Ah, yes, as I was going to say,
we have no venue suitable
for such an esteemed guest.
That's already settled.
There's a lady
I met in the capital
with a house
she'll let me borrow.
And how much is this
going to cost us?
[PHILIP]
It's free.
And it isn't a scam?
Don't worry, it's fine.
She said she saw my potential
and wanted to invest
in me. It's that easy.
Which house is this lady from?
Surely, I would know her.
She's just a commoner,
judging from her name.
But she's a very
wealthy commoner.
Hilma Cygnaeus.
Does that name ring a bell?
[NOBLES chattering, laughing]
I'm the host tonight, not you.
[NOBLE 402B]
Thank you for the invitation!
I'm delighted!
[NOBLE 402C]
Lady Hilma!
Why are all the guests
greeting her instead of me?
You seem displeased,
Lord Philip, what is the matter?
Nothing, I was deep
in thought, that's all.
Remember, I'm your
willing partner.
One that wants to share in
the taste of your sweet success.
There's no benefit in hiding
the truth from me.
As you asked, I left
the invitations to you,
but I feel like many of our
guests are unqualified.
[HILMA] There aren't
many influential figures
in the traditional sense, no.
I mostly chose to
invite heirs who were
newly appointed after
the war, like you.
Will I be able to create a new
faction with these people?
They're mostly powerless.
But that's the whole point!
Because they'll grow in power
under your expert leadership.
Yes, a fine point.
[PHILIP]
This is good.
All I have to do
is show the way,
and those fools will
fall in line soon enough.
[PHILIP] She's truly the most
beautiful woman I've ever seen,
and she smells lovely, too!
Tonight, I have gathered
nobles who wish to become
closer with the
Sorcerer Kingdom.
Everyone here is
greatly looking forward
to meeting you, Lady Albedo!
Thank you for all your
support, Lord Philip.
Seems you've worked hard!
[gasps]
Just out of curiosity,
do you happen to be
married, Lady Albedo?
What an interesting
question to ask.
Unfortunately, I'm single.
And a bit lonely, I must say.
What a shame.
[ANNOUNCER 402A]
Announcing the arrival
of the Sorcerer Kingdom's
envoy, Lady Albedo!
[metal whirring]
Is something the matter?
What? No!
Let's proceed! They're waiting!
[HILMA] Third-rate nobles
in a first-class venue,
look at the stupid grins
on their faces.
They have no clue
this is a feeding ground.
Hilma, seems Lady Albedo
would like to rest a bit.
The whole ball's
lined up to talk to her.
Anyone would be
exhausted after all that.
You can get back to mingling.
I'll escort her to the
sitting room for you.
Actually, I'll come along, too.
I don't think that
would be a good idea.
And why not?
I'm the host of
the ball, aren't I?
It's not proper for a man
to accompany a lady
to the sitting room
unless he's her husband.
Oh, right. That makes sense.
Speaking of which.
If I were to court Lady Albedo,
how do you think I should
I go about that?
[gasps]
I managed to bring all of
these nobles together, didn't I?
And while the Sorcerer Kingdom
has a strong army,
they only possess a single city.
So, my social status
is comparable to hers.
Don't you agree?
Hilma?
No, stop!
It will never happen,
and be careful what you say
about the Sorcerer Kingdom!
But you saw us when we walked
in. We have a great rapport!
That worm. He got
his filth on me.
There's only one
man in the world
allowed to touch
my body like that.
Only one man who's
allowed to lust over me!
That shit! That lowly
piece of excrement!
Even I was shocked
by that fool's audacity.
I'd be happy to prepare a new
puppet if you wish, Lady Albedo.
I'm just complaining.
It would be a waste, since he's
already made an impression
on the other nobles
with those antics of his.
Do you think he's acting
stupid on purpose?
It's difficult to say.
[HILMA]
This is it.
[SMUGGLING LEADER 402A]
Lady Albedo,
we have been
waiting for you.
[ALBEDO]
I'll get straight to the point.
The Sorcerer Kingdom needs food
and other daily necessities
delivered immediately.
[SMUGGLING LEADER 402A]
Understood.
We will assemble
a proper tribute.
[ALBEDO]
No. That's not what I meant.
Sell the items for
a reasonable price,
and with the money you make,
prepare countermeasures
for the kingdom's
inevitable food shortage.
Now, how is your magic
item research going?
[ALBEDO]
You may raise your head.
[RENNER]
Thank you.
Oh, my.
Lord Ains is quite
satisfied with your work.
He's prepared a fitting
reward I think you'll enjoy.
I'm so happy.
Thank you, Lady Albedo.
And please give my
regards to His Majesty.
I owe Lord Ains
my deepest gratitude.
What lovely manners!
I assume we don't need to
discuss your other request?
You understand the conditions?
Oh, yes, I do.
Nothing in the world
would make me happier
than to receive such
a kindness from you.
After the proper price
is paid, of course.
That box will grant your wish,
but will you be able to open it?
Yes. I've already
begun preparations.
I see.
Just make sure everything's
ready before the invasion.
I'm sure you're capable.
[RENNER]
Understood, Your Greatness.
I think that's enough
formal discussion for now.
The night's young.
While I'm here, why don't you
tell me a little bit more
about your puppy?
I'd love to, Lady Albedo.
And could you tell me
more about Lord Ains?
I'm sure you have all sorts
of charming stories
about His Majesty to share!