[ALBEDO sighs]
Lord Momonga.
It's the glorious dawn
of the Sorcerer Kingdom.
But what form shall it take?
What country shall Lord Ains
forge in his boundless wisdom?
It matters not.
Whatever your vision may be,
it is my sworn
duty to follow it.
Please, My Lord. Show it to me.
Oh! Show me everything,
Lord Ains!
[AINS]
It is time.
[FOIRE]
Yes, My Lord!
I will submit my report and
change shifts with today's maid.
Is there anything else you need?
[AINS]
I only ask that you rest well.
You worked hard,
staying up all night.
That's very kind
of you, My Lord!
I'm grateful, but it's my job
to serve you the best I can!
Don't worry about me!
[MOMONGA] They're really
not taking a hint.
[AINS]
Oops.
How do I tell them these bedside
shifts are a bit excessive?
What a pain.
[MOMONGA] What if I said that
I didn't want servants at all?
That I wanted us to be equals?
'Scuse me, Lord Ains!
Good morning!
--I will be assisting you today.
--[MOMONGA] Maybe...
Maybe if we did that, it would
be like the good old days.
It would be like having
my friends back.
First off, let's get
you dressed.
What would you
like to wear today?
[AINS]
Here's an idea.
Why don't you decide, Fith?
That's perfect!
I know just the look!
Leave it to me!
You'll be thrilled!
[AINS] I hate to question
your expertise,
but I do worry that this robe
might be a bit gaudy for me.
There's no need to be
insecure, trust me!
A lesser ruler might
look pretentious
with all those jewels but you
can definitely pull this off!
Your black cloak certainly
has a wonderful mystique,
but it's nice to see
you in other colors!
[AINS]
Good morning, Nurunuru.
Time for breakfast.
[FITH]
Lord Ains.
Lady Albedo and the
Elder Liches are here.
[AINS]
Very well. You may let them in.
Greetings, My Lord.
It's a pleasure, as always.
What a dashing ensemble
you're wearing!
Why, it seems
as if it's glowing!
But these fine jewels
wouldn't shine so brightly
if they adorned anyone but you.
[AINS] Well, thank you
for the kind words, Albedo.
But I was merely
stating the truth!
I would never engage in
meaningless flattery, My Lord!
It's only natural that--
[AINS]
I get the idea.
Moving onto the
business at hand.
These are the documents
you put together last night?
Correct.
[MOMONGA] Nope. I don't
understand any of this.
I'm just an office worker--
Not even management!
There's no way I can
run an entire kingdom.
But I can't exactly
tell them that, now can I?
I'll just pretend to read these,
so I look the part at least.
Okay, last one.
Huh. What is this?
It's a report about
some materials, I think.
But the details don't
make any sense to me.
Did something catch
your attention?
[AINS]
No, just lost in thought.
More importantly,
have you constructed
a code of law for the kingdom?
I've discussed the
matter with Demiurge,
but we've only come up
with an initial draft.
[AINS] I speak with confidence
in many subjects,
but when it comes to
social law, I regret to say
that I'm not very knowledgeable.
But a supreme ruler such
as you commands all laws!
[gasps] I see!
You didn't bother learning any
laws, because you're above them,
so they're meaningless to you!
[AINS]
Yes, uh, naturally.
So, I'll allow you to
proceed as you see fit.
I believe in you.
[gasps] Thank you!
I'll do my very best!
Is something wrong?
[AINS]
I didn't mean to stare.
Your smile was so cute,
it caught me off guard.
Excuse me, I can't
find the words.
This is terribly awkward.
[ALBEDO]
Oh, my! I'm so embarrassed!
[AINS]
Ahem! Moving on.
[gasps]
[AINS]
Let's handle our usual business.
These are various proposals
from the people of Nazarick.
I am going through
them personally
so that they remain anonymous.
[MOMONGA] That way I can
sneak in my own ideas, too!
[AINS]
Here's the first one.
"I think it would be good
to set up an educational
system for the children.
If we find and raise
talented individuals,
they will continue to strengthen
Nazarick for years to come."
Interesting.
Most likely from Yuri Alpha.
It is a foolish suggestion.
Pigs do not need knowledge.
All they need to do is
live, breathe, and die
for their master.
[AINS]
I agree in a sense, at least.
Knowledge is worth more
when it's monopolized.
But that's only one way
to look at the situation.
I think the proposal could
work out quite well, actually.
[gasps]
[AINS] Although it's not exactly
what Yuri had in mind,
I think we can salvage the play
by establishing an
orphanage in E-Rantel.
A more traditional school
may open Nazarick's secrets
and technology to espionage.
But if we pull prospective
students from the orphanage,
we can guarantee that
only the most talented
and loyal candidates
are elevated.
The orphanage itself can be
run by the war widows
created in the recent conflict.
So, not only will you
give children a home,
you'll also give jobs
to poverty-stricken women.
The masses will
surely applaud this.
Your popularity
will rise quickly.
[AINS] Then have Pestonya and
Nigredo attend to the matter.
Release them from house arrest
as soon as we're done here.
Perhaps I should
remind you, My Lord.
During our attack on the
capital, they were ordered
to kill the humans
that you captured.
To maintain the secrecy
of Jaldabaoth's
relationship to Nazarick.
Quite simple.
And yet those two
went against your orders.
They sheltered
an infant in secret.
Never mind their house arrest,
they should be executed
for their foul treachery.
[AINS]
Albedo...
Oh, please, My Lord.
Don't look at me with
that piercing gaze!
[AINS]
Huh?
[sighs] But your
orders are absolute.
I won't question them further.
I will release those two
from house arrest.
[AINS] And don't execute
them afterwards, please.
Of course.
[AINS]
Now, the next proposal.
"I would like to suggest
making uniforms
to give Nazarick a
stronger sense of unity."
An exceedingly
tasteless proposal.
Who suggested such a thing?
[MOMONGA]
I'm sorry! It was me!
Let me look into this matter.
The perpetrator must
face punishment.
[AINS] These are supposed
to be anonymous!
Also, when I asked
everyone for suggestions,
I promised there would
be no repercussions!
Fine, then.
[knocking]
You have guests!
It's Lady Aura and Lord Mare.
[AINS]
Let them in.
I missed you!
Good morning, Lord Ains!
[MARE]
Um, good morning, My Lord.
I like your robe.
[AINS]
Thank you, I suppose.
[AURA]
Good morning, Albedo!
Is something wrong?
You didn't make
an appointment first, so--
Hey! Wait!
[AINS]
Ah, is this what you wanted?
Huh?! His lap? How dare you!
It's no big deal!
He doesn't mind!
[AINS]
You can come, too.
Well, My Lord.
With your permission?
Is there room for me?
[AINS]
Albedo, please. You're an adult.
[ALBEDO squeals]
[AINS]
Don't mind her.
What brings you here?
No reason. We just
wanted to see you!
[AINS] Very well, then.
I'm happy to see you, too.
[ALBEDO]
Lord Ains. What if I was a baby?
[AINS]
Hm?
[mimicking baby cry]
You know, I think I've had
enough lap time for today.
Here. Why don't you
take my spot?
[AINS]
That's very generous of you.
All right, Albedo, come here.
Thank you!
[AINS]
You can sit on my lap,
but I'm not going
to pick you up.
[MOMONGA]
So soft.
And wait. What's that fragrance?
Is there a problem, My Lord?
[AINS] I was just admiring
your lovely smell.
If you'd like to sniff me some
more, by all means, be my guest!
Sniff me for an hour
or sniff all day!
[AINS] An hour is a bit
excessive, I think.
[ALBEDO whines]
[AINS] Though, perhaps
I could sniff for a bit.
[MOMONGA] It smells
so familiar--what is it?
[AURA]
Lord Ains.
It looks really pervy
when you do that.
[AINS]
Oh. Sorry.
All right, we've had our fun.
Get down.
But this isn't fair.
Aura got on much
earlier than me!
I deserve more time!
Stop whining! You get to spend
way more time with
him than we do!
That's only natural, isn't it?
I have to for work.
Oh, I see! So, it's just a job!
Whereas I came here to visit
Lord Ain's because I wanted to!
[MOMONGA] Albedo's one thing,
but why's Aura acting like this?
[MOMONGA]
Maybe she lacks a father figure
and she wants more
attention from me?
This environment
isn't exactly ideal
for someone's
emotional development.
Maybe there's a kingdom of
dark elves they could visit
and make some friends.
Um, are you angry?
[AINS] Sorry, no, not at all.
My mind was wandering.
Worried about that
issue from before?
[AINS]
Yes, that's right. Naturally.
[MOMONGA]
What issue?!
I've given it some thought,
and I have a couple of
suggestions that
could be helpful.
[AINS]
I would expect nothing less!
Wait, is something bad going on?
Let's tell them.
They might have some
good ideas of their own.
[AINS]
I agree.
Please explain it to them
in a simple manner.
In a way that's
easy to understand.
For their sake, of course.
Also get off my lap.
All right.
Simply put, there's
not enough trade.
E-Rantel is facing
a shortage of goods.
That sounds bad.
[MOMONGA]
Uh-oh!
It must have been
in that document.
Until recently, E-Rantel was
a vital city of commerce.
But the sudden shift in power
seems to have worried merchants.
We have precious
little outside trade.
The amount of goods in
circulation keeps dropping.
So, what should we do?
We don't need to worry about it.
I'm sure Lord Ains
will fix everything.
Yeah! Right!
[AINS] Albedo, have we
taken any action yet?
We have. With any luck,
we'll be reaping the seeds
that Demiurge sowed in no time.
[AINS]
I see.
[MOMONGA] I'm sure
he has it under control,
but I thought he
was busy setting up
plans in the Holy Kingdom.
In the meantime,
I have a small matter
I need to attend to as well.
With your permission,
I'd like to go to the
Re-Estize Kingdom for now.
[AINS]
What? But you're responsible
for all of Nazarick's
domestic affairs.
That might be tough.
I promise I'll return
as soon as possible.
Pandora's Actor can take my
place for a while, can't he?
[AINS]
I suppose that might work.
I'll speak with him directly
about the matter.
I trust your judgement.
I expect good results.
And as for Demiurge...
No, never mind.
[AINS]
Now, let's continue.
Since the two of you are here,
I'll listen to your
opinions, as well.
[MARE]
Opinions on what?
[AINS]
On anything.
I'm looking for ideas to
improve the Sorcerer Kingdom.
Speak freely.
[AURA] Ooh! In that case,
I have a great idea!
[AINS]
Oh? Go ahead.
I think that all of the boys
should dress up like girls!
And all of the girls
should dress like boys,
as required by law!
Yes. I agree. That sounds good.
[MOMONGA]
Bukubuku Chagama, why?
That was a close call!
Even if it's a
degenerate indulgence,
Albedo won't question one
of the "Supreme Beings."
If I hadn't convinced
the twins that their creator
wanted them to be unique,
the kingdom would've taken
quite the turn!
[AINS]
Hm.
Wake up, Hamusuke.
Huh? Is it morning, already?
Oh! Hey there, Master of mine!
[AINS]
Call me Lord Ains in public.
Remember, you're the riding
beast of the great hero Momon.
That I am, Master. Yes, sir!
[AINS] So, why is that
Death Knight with you?
We're training partners, we are,
so we're together all the time!
[AINS]
Oh, that's right.
We were experimenting to see
if you two could
obtain Martial Arts.
[AINS]
Well, never mind that.
I'm looking for Momon
or rather, Pandora's Actor.
Have business with your
body double, do you?
He should be in that
building over there.
[PANDORA'S ACTOR]
Oh, Supreme One!
My dear, beloved
creator, Lord Ains!
[AINS]
Greetings are not necessary.
Sit.
[PANDORA'S ACTOR]
Sir! Hut! Hut! Hut! Hut!
[MOMONGA]
Uh-- Come on!
There's an empty seat
right across from me!
[PANDORA'S ACTOR]
What's wrong? Tell me!
[MOMONGA]
So intimate!
[AINS] There's no reason
to be so uppity.
I just need to go over
a few things with you.
First of all, how are you faring
as Momon's body double?
[PANDORA'S ACTOR]
No issues, sir! In fact I--
[AINS]
Good! Good!
Do you have any other concerns?
[PANDORA'S ACTOR] Actually,
there is something.
It's a tragedy!
I haven't touched
a magic item in ages!
That means no
regular maintenance
and no organizing our
data crystals, either!
Work left undone!
You must rectify
this matter, My Lord!
Let me touch them!
Just for a moment!
Those sweet magic items!
[AINS] Did I really
make you so emotional?
[PANDORA'S ACTOR]
Yes! These feelings
overflowing from my heart
were a gift from you!
[AINS] Of course. It's all
coming back to me now.
[PANDORA'S ACTOR] Please allow
me to return to the treasury
and fulfill my only
purpose in life!
[AINS] I understand.
Let me speak to Shalltear.
I'll have her get
a teleportation ring
for you, all right?
--[PANDORA'S ACTOR] Sir, yes--
--[AINS] No. Stop. Stop.
I understand that your manner
of speech is my doing, probably.
But I have a suggestion.
Although I don't
recall why I set you
to these specifications,
I'm honored
that you've stuck
to them so diligently.
However, I also believe
that a child should surpass
the expectations
of their parents.
[PANDORA'S ACTOR] Lord Ains!
You see me as your child?
[AINS]
Indeed, I do.
Thus, there's no need to salute
or act quite so
extravagantly before me.
[PANDORA'S ACTOR]
Ah, of course.
[AINS] I want to see you do
new and different things.
Things that exceed
my imagination!
I want to see your growth
as an individual!
[AINS]
Huh?
[PANDORA'S ACTOR]
I understand, Father!
I will abide by your wishes
and blossom into
a beautiful new "me"!
[AINS]
Good.
Wait! Actually, one more thing.
Do as you like,
but don't mention
this conversation to anyone.
There will be unrest
if the others think
I give you
preferential treatment.
[PANDORA'S ACTOR]
Right.
[AINS] That goes for
you as well, Fith.
[AINS]
I will take my leave now.
[PANDORA'S ACTOR]
One moment.
There's is something I want
to ask you, if you don't mind.
What kind of ruler do you intend
to be in this new
kingdom of yours?
Many people come to Momon with
trepidation in their hearts.
They ask what will
become of this country,
what will become of them.
Will they be forced
to work like slaves?
Will they be sent off
to fight in a war?
[AINS] What form should
the Sorcerer Kingdom take?
[AINS] Undead servants are
naturally quite productive.
They require neither sleep
nor rest, after all.
But I wonder.
Fith, what do you think
about this country?
[FITH]
Well, My Lord,
thanks to your
wisdom as a ruler,
life here is easy
and convenient.
However, it troubles
me that no one
comes running to worship you.
They hide when you show
your reverent figure.
I don't understand why they
would do such a shameful thing.
[AINS] I see. And what
do you think of humans?
Do you find them to be insipid?
I do.
They weren't created by any of
the supreme beings, after all.
They're wretched creatures.
[MOMONGA] It seems like all
the NPCs see humans as inferior,
as misguided as that is.
I used to hear the same sorts
of things from Narberal.
She called humans "worms"
when we traveled together.
Huh. Haven't been
to the guild in a while.
[AINS]
Is no one here?
[DESK ATTENDANT 401A]
Oh! Greetings, Your Majesty!
[AINS]
Not many quests, available.
Yes, I'm terribly
sorry, My Lord.
[AINS]
I'm not blaming you.
I was just curious.
The board used to be
overflowing with jobs.
At least, that's what I heard
from the adventurer, Momon.
Yes, that's true.
But monster hunting and security
quests are no longer necessary.
So, personal requests are
the only thing available now.
[AINS]
In other words, my undead forces
are properly
maintaining the peace.
[MOMONGA] Adventuring isn't
all it was cracked up to be,
so that's for the best.
[AINS]
Is the guild master in?
Yes, of course!
Wait just a moment and I'll let
him know that you're here.
[AINZACH] Your Majesty,
it's an honor for you to visit
this humble establishment.
Forgive me for offering
such a meagre welcome.
[AINS]
Let's talk, Ainzach.
I'm surprised the
Sorcerer King knows the name
of a commoner like me.
[AINS]
Of course.
[MOMONGA]
I feel like a sleazy salesman,
but I have to get him
on board for this to work.
Is there something on your mind?
[AINS]
Ah. I'll cut to the chase.
I'd like to absorb
the adventurer's guild
into the Sorcerer Kingdom.
Well, then no one will stop you.
[AINS]
Is that so?
I heard that the
adventurer guilds don't like
to align themselves
with any nation.
You have no objections?
I won't protest.
[AINS]
Mm. No, that's too easy.
I imagine you'll
tell the adventurers
to leave the kingdom.
Then, once they've all
cleared out, you'll hand me
an empty shell of
an organization.
[AINS]
Tell me this.
Why is it that
the adventurer guilds
never involve themselves
with the government?
It's quite simple.
Because adventurers exist
to protect the people. If we
lent our strength in a war,
then that would
betray our purpose.
[AINS] Hmph. Your duty
is to protect the people?
And how would you
define "people," exactly?
Do you only mean humans?
I don't follow, My Lord.
[AINS]
What about elves and half-elves?
Races that live
alongside humans?
Well, yes. They're
included, of course.
[AINS] Aren't elves treated
as slaves in the Empire?
It doesn't sound like
you're protecting them.
What about other
intelligent creatures?
Ones with less "traditionally
appealing" forms, I mean.
Like lizard men,
orcs, and goblins?
Your Majesty.
Those are subhumans.
Are you trying to mock me?
[AINS] Hm. As an undead,
they're not much different
than humans to me.
[AINS]
Well, have a seat.
Listen to my proposal.
[AINS]
To me, the ideal adventurer
is not a mere fighter,
but someone who
explores the unknown.
And through that
exploration, they have
the unique opportunity to make
our world a better place.
Can you elaborate, please?
[AINS] Until now, most of your
jobs were monster hunting
or security details--
Mercenary work.
But there is no need for that
in the Sorcerer Kingdom.
My subordinates are tireless
and much stronger
than the average adventurer.
But while they're quite adept
at killing, I'm not confident
they would do as well
charting a course
into unknown lands.
Especially if the goal
is to establish amicable
relations with the people there.
Embarrassing, I know.
Your Majesty.
That's why I want adventurers
to take up this role.
I can protect the kingdom,
they will explore beyond it.
Why not simply post a request?
I don't see why the government
needs to get involved in this.
If I post my request and
problems arise between
unknown races or countries,
will the guild be able
to resolve these
issues on their own?
Since you're an
independent body,
the kingdom would
disavow any involvement.
But since you exist in my
territory, I won't tolerate
any actions that cause
this kingdom harm.
That's awful.
[AINS] Which is why I need
to take the adventurer's guild
under my wing if
I want this to succeed.
But this is an
important operation,
so I vow to give you
my complete support.
There's something I need
to get straight, first.
You talk about exploring
new lands, but are you only
doing that because you intend
to invade them later?
[AINS] That's not the plan,
but I can't make any promises.
If we find a nation that is an
imminent threat to our kingdom,
we may need to take action.
Fair enough.
[AINS]
And consider this.
I have enough military power
to do all the invading I choose.
I don't expect adventurers to
gather intel and chart a course
for that, when I have
more effective means.
As things stand now,
adventurers are simply
glorified exterminators. I want
to elevate them beyond that.
I want them to embody
the spirit their title invokes.
Your guild will be reborn!
You will become adventurers,
in the true sense of the word!
It is a very compelling
offer, Your Majesty.
I do admit.
Count me in.
You brought a spark back
to this old adventurer.
The unknown's calling for us
and it's time to answer.
[AINS]
Fith.
My Lord?
[AINS]
There's nothing I treasure more
than servants like you.
You're the creations left
behind by my beloved comrades.
I'm honored you think that!
[AINS] But I must bestow love
upon those I rule over as well.
This is my kingdom, after all.
I must show it proper
care and affection.
Absolutely, My Lord, I agree!
[AINS]
Then, let us create a utopia.
A land as sweet as honey--
a dream that never ends.
A kingdom where the
people bow before me
in reverence and gratitude.
How wonderful! I can
hardly wait to see it!
[AINS] But this will not be
a utopia for humans alone.
All humanoid races shall
flourish beneath my banner
and all non-humanoid
races as well!
We shall let the world know.
Eternal prosperity can only
be found under the rule
of the Sorcerer Kingdom!
[MOMONGA]
This is my purpose!
I'll recreate the guild of Ains
Ooal Gown here in this world.
And if my comrades are
still out there somewhere,
then maybe they'll take notice
and I can show them my work
with pride in my heart.