[ANNOUNCER 3A]
And here he is at last,
making his dramatic return!
It's the hero of the colosseum,
the most powerful fighter
in all the land!
Let's hear it for
the Warrior King!
[AINS] Forget everything
you've seen today.
Of course, My Lord.
[MOMONGA] There's no doubt that
Nazarick is an overwhelmingly
powerful force,
but I still worry.
There's an enemy out there
with a world item and
we don't know where.
The "world domination approach"
has gone well enough
and I know that's what
everyone else wants.
[AINS] But I must bestow love
upon those I rule over as well,
this is my kingdom, after all.
I must show it proper
care and affection.
Absolutely, My Lord, I agree!
[AINS]
Then, let us create a utopia.
A land as sweet as honey,
a dream that never ends.
A carrot and stick
approach, perhaps?
[MOMONGA] Come to think of it,
I might be onto something.
I could even see this bringing
us some good publicity,
which is exactly what I need
to recruit adventurers!
[AINS]
What a splendid idea.
Pardon, Your Majesty?
This city looks familiar.
If I may ask, is this Arwintar,
the Imperial Capital?
[AINS]
That is correct.
I-I see.
Then is there a reason we didn't
pass through a check point?
[AINS]
A trivial detail.
Kings entering other
countries unannounced
is an international issue!
[AINS]
Do not fret.
Master El Nix and I
are on good terms.
I'm sure that he will
look the other way.
If you say so.
[MOMONGA] There's good
reason for our secrecy.
If Jircniv knew I was coming,
he'd throw a formal
welcome for sure.
Last thing I need
is for him to find out
I know nothing
about noble society.
I intentionally used a
Gate spell so that we could
sneak into their country
on the downlow.
Excuse my bluntness,
but what are you
planning to do here
now that we've arrived?
I think it's time
that I learn the plan.
[AINS] I intend to invite
the adventurers from the Empire
to my kingdom.
You're saying this
is a recruiting mission?
[AINS]
Indeed.
There is potential.
However, are you sure they
would uproot their lives
and leave everything
they gained behind?
This will be a hard sell.
It's a lot to ask of people.
[AINS]
Hm.
[MOMONGA] This is exactly
the sort of opinion
I wanted to hear.
Sorry if I overstepped
my boundaries.
[AINS]
No, no.
I am a different type
of entity from you.
That's why some of
my reactions may vary
from those of a
typical human being.
Please continue to voice your
concerns so that I may adapt.
All right. Then
allow me to add this.
You mentioned previously that
you want to have adventurers
to explore the unknown, correct?
And that you would give us
your unconditional support
for that purpose?
Then I must ask, does
that generous offer extend
to the new recruits as well
as the ones we have now?
[AINS]
That is my intention.
Creating an institute
to nurture adventurers
is the point, after all.
I didn't realize
you thought that far.
Then, wouldn't it be a good idea
to gather and raise
some fledglings?
[AINS]
Hm...
People admire the
strong, don't they?
This is the Imperial Capital.
Why not publicize your mission
by showing off your power
at the colosseum?
[AINS]
Ah. Now that is a clever idea.
Do take note.
The Empire has an
infamous champion.
"Warrior King" he's called.
[AINS] That is quite a
hefty moniker, indeed.
He's the current title holder,
and although he's the eighth man
to carry that name,
he's the strongest so far.
I just so happen to be
acquaintances with his promoter.
And if you like, I can arrange
a meeting with him for you.
[MOMONGA]
Look at the size of that place!
This guy must be rolling in it!
Then again, he is the promoter
for the greatest champ
the colosseum has ever known,
I'm sure that's
pretty lucrative.
Looking good.
As requested, I've set up
a meeting with him for you.
So be ready by 10 o'clock
tomorrow morning.
I imagine we could
squeeze in sooner, though.
If he knew it was you asking
for a private audience,
he might swing for it right now.
[AINS]
That won't be necessary.
We should be thankful he's
available to see us so quickly.
[gasps]
[AINS]
What is it?
It's nothing.
I was thinking how
impressed I was
by your patience, Your Majesty.
[AINS] Mm. Anyway, I will have
you accompany me again tomorrow.
In the meantime, please
enjoy the evening off.
I'll send you back to E-Rantel
by using a bit of magic.
Greater Teleportation.
[gasps]
[AINS]
All right.
I'll take this time
to now contact Fluder.
I wanted to look into something.
[FLUDER]
Why, hello!
So good of you to visit,
my radiant Lord!
[AINS] So, Fluder, have
my orders been carried out?
[FLUDER] Yes! As requested,
I have finished
recording the data for
the nearby countries.
However, I encountered
one problem
that may cause some concern.
The emperor has discovered
my betrayal, unfortunately.
[AINS]
That's hardly unexpected.
But don't worry,
I'll simply adjust our
next course of action.
Please be seated.
[FLUDER]
Very well.
Huh? What is that?
[AINS]
It's your reward.
With this, I shall bestow a
piece of my wisdom upon thee.
[FLUDER]
My apologies.
It seems I am unable
to decipher this.
[AINS]
Mm. In that case, try this.
[FLUDER]
Thank you!
[MOMONGA]
Hope this is a good gift.
I doubt it even applies
to the magic in this world,
but at least the
cover looks fancy.
[FLUDER gasps]
Incredible! It says here
that human souls
are like droplets
that have separated from
the river of the greater world.
While the size of the soul
may be varying in size,
they all originate from
the same source!
What a breakthrough!
Now, this is truly fascinating!
It is exactly the knowledge
I have been seeking! Wow!
[AINS] Splendid. I'll
take my eyeglass now.
It's my only one, so I
can't just give it to you.
But I'll need it for the future.
[AINS] You'll only be able
to ascend to the next realm
of knowledge when you
can translate, decipher,
and understand the text.
Very well, My Lord.
I shall not fight you
on that logic.
[AINS]
Thank you.
Now, please divulge what
you know of the Warrior King.
Quite a rare sight.
A female Rabbit Man.
They come from far east of here.
[BUTLER 4A]
This way, if you would.
You may enter.
[OSK]
Does what you see please you?
[AINS] Yes. This is
quite the collection.
Anything happen
to catch your eye?
Ah, that one, maybe?
[AINS]
May I hold it?
[OSK]
Of course.
[AINS]
Interesting. Are these runes?
I'd expect nothing less
from the Sorcerer King!
Are these familiar to you?
[MOMONGA]
Dang, so they actually are?
I wonder if a player
spread the knowledge.
[AINS]
This is a fine work.
Who created it?
This was made
in a rune workshop,
by a dwarven craftsman.
They have a kingdom in the
Azerlisia mountain range.
[AINS]
Ah, how intriguing.
So tell me, Osk.
How did you know
it was His Majesty?
I'm surprised you
figured it out so easily.
Honestly, it really
wasn't that hard
to put two and two together.
If you, the head of
the adventurer's guild,
is reporting to someone,
only one person from
E-Rantell comes to mind.
Allow me to introduce myself.
My name is Osk,
I'm just a humble merchant.
It's truly an honor to meet you.
[AINS]
As you have surmised,
I am the Sorcerer King,
Ains Ooal Gown.
In all your glory!
But I'm shocked!
What could someone
such as me provide
to a ruler of such
extraordinary influence?
[AINS]
I would like to battle
the Warrior King
in the colosseum.
Funny joke, sir. A knee slapper.
[AINS]
I'm serious.
Do correct me if I'm wrong,
but are you not the
ruler of a country?
[AINS]
I am.
Apologies. Please understand,
the complications are too many.
[AINS]
Do not fret.
No matter what happens to me,
I promise it won't
cause you any trouble.
I can put it in writing,
if you like.
Let me confirm something then.
I gather a lot of information,
especially about the
warriors and monsters
I plan to have appear
in the colosseum.
Among the rumors, one in
particular concerned you.
Is it true that you annihilated
tens of thousands of people
from the Kingdom
using a single magic spell?
[AINS]
Uh, yes.
That spell is... Oh, right!
That magic is more like a trump
card I rarely like to use.
It was Master Jircniv's wish,
so I had no choice
but to use a major
spell like that.
It's one I can only cast
once every ten years.
To use it again would take
at least a decade.
Ah. Are you sure it's okay
you divulged that detail
with someone like me?
In a way, you revealed a weak
point to me, Your Majesty.
[AINS]
Please.
It's not as if all
my magic is incapacitated.
Fair enough, I s'pose!
One last question then.
Why would a powerful ruler
of a country, such as yourself,
want to fight against
the Warrior King?
[AINS] Well, the rumor is,
he was someone strong,
so it piqued my curiosity.
I'd like to find out
if he is stronger than
Gazef Stronoff, for one.
Then I understand.
I shall prepare a match
with the Warrior King
right away for you, sir.
But King or no King,
there are certain rules
you'll have to follow
in the colosseum.
[AINS]
That's reasonable.
For instance, we will want
you to fight him with
only weapons and zero
magic, Your Majesty.
But the king is clearly
a magic caster!
[AINS]
That's fine by me.
[AINZACH, OSK gasp]
[AINS] I swear upon my name,
Ains Ooal Gown,
that I will not use magic
when fighting the Warrior King.
You have my word.
[OSK]
Headhunter Rabbit.
Yes, sir?
What's your honest opinion on
His Majesty, the Sorcerer King?
One glance and I wanted
to run for my life.
[RABBIT] What are you
gawking at, you creep?
I just noticed
your lovely hands.
Don't take it the wrong way.
Besides, I'm more interested
in someone like Gargaran,
the warrior from Blue Rose.
If you had a little more height
and meat on you, then maybe.
I guess I won't be renewing
my contract next year.
That aside, could Lord Ains win?
Honestly.
It's gonna be an
absolute bloodbath.
[ANNOUNCER 3A] Now, our
next challenger is a name
I'm sure you'll recognize!
King of the Sorcerer Kingdom...
[OSK] How are we feeling,
Warrior King?
[WARRIOR KING]
I'm feeling grateful.
Thanks to you
keeping your promises,
I've become as
strong as I am now.
I'm in tip-top condition.
Very well.
[WARRIOR KING growls]
[OSK]
There he goes.
Good luck.
[CROWD cheering]
[JIRCNIV]
Come on, Warrior King!
We're rooting for you!
[WARRIOR KING]
I am the war troll,
known as the
Warrior King, Go Gin!
[AINS] And I am Ains Ooal Gown,
the Sorcerer King.
The highest-class of undead.
In other words, an Overlord.
[WARRIOR KING]
I see.
Then I will fight you
with all my might!
[AINS] Oh? You're not going
to make fun of my name?
I thought that your race found
long names to be ostentatious.
[WARRIOR KING]
Ah, didn't expect that.
I see you're quite familiar
with war trolls.
However, I would never mock
the name of the strong!
[AINS]
My mistake.
I suppose that means I
should readjust how I think
when it comes to your people.
[WARRIOR KING laughs]
Not necessary.
I'm an outlier.
Besides, regardless of race,
there's always a
diversity of thought.
[AINS laughs]
Right you are.
I'm starting to grow
fond of you, Warrior King.
Will you join my side
should I win?
[WARRIOR KING] Sure. If I
lose, I'll pledge my loyalty.
However, should I claim victory,
I wish to eat you.
[AINS]
Huh?
[WARRIOR KING]
Until now, I've never met anyone
worth killing
and devouring.
But you're more powerful
than I am, so if I eat you,
I can absorb your essence
and become even stronger.
[AINS]
That's fine by me.
Either way, the victor holds
the other's life in their hands.
But do me just one
favor, all right?
Allow Resurrection
if I kill you.
[CROWD cheers]
Rip 'im apart, Warrior King!
[WARRIOR KING yells]
[AINS]
Are you using martial arts?
[JIRCNIV] You got this!
Let's see some blood!
[AINS laughs]
You're an interesting one.
I do question
that stance though.
Are you inviting me to strike?
I'd be obliged!
[WARRIOR KING groans]
[AINS] As expected,
he's distracted by fire.
It does inhibit a war troll's
healing capabilities, after all.
However...
[JIRCNIV] You've got him
in a good position!
[MOMONGA]
Our countries are supposed to be
in an alliance, you jerk!
As an allied king,
you could at least
show a little concern for me!
[AINS] I can emit negative
energy and impart it to you
with a mere touch.
[WARRIOR KING]
This--This isn't poison?
[AINS]
No, because you would be able
to recover from that with
your regeneration powers.
As I'm sure you've noticed,
my powers have weakened
your strength and agility.
While trolls can
easily heal injuries,
I doubt you can heal
your loss of ability.
In this battle, we are
prohibited from using magic.
However, that did not include
the use of magic items.
I didn't want to give myself
too big of an advantage,
so I limited what I brought.
[AINS] This is a weapon
I borrowed from Momon.
Now, shall we continue?
[WARRIOR KING yells]
[WARRIOR KING]
Again?
Hide Reinforcement!
Greater Hide Reinforcement!
[AINS]
Activate!
[WARRIOR KING groans]
[MOMONGA]
That's weird.
I'd hoped more people would
be cheering for me by now.
[AINS] I suppose it's tough
being the away team.
Let's wrap this up.
Next, I'm killing you.
If you admit defeat,
we avoid that, of course.
[WARRIOR KING]
No. I'm still the Warrior King!
When I claimed that title,
this became my resting place.
[AINS] Then take off that helmet
and show me your face.
[AINS]
Those eyes. Determined.
Let me ask you.
Can you make a comeback?
What techniques do you
have left to beat me?
None, but it's not over!
Beat me proper!
[AINS]
Then, come at me, Warrior King!
[roars]
[AINS]
You have speed, but that's all.
Aura of Despair. Level 1!
Strong Strike!
Divine Skill, Single Flash!
Flow Acceleration!
[yells]
[WARRIOR KING]
Dammit!
[AINS] No techniques left
to defeat me, huh?
I was tricked.
Punitto Moe would scold me.
Hurry up! You can
still win, Warrior King!
[AINS]
Jeez, he's loud.
[MOMONGA]
Jircniv, what the hell?
I hear you clear
as day, you know!
[AINS] Though you are
the better fighter,
there is one insurmountable
difference between.
[WARRIOR KING yells]
[WARRIOR KING groans]
[AINS]
Unlike you, I am level 100.
My HP will long outlast yours.
[AINS]
Hm. Dropping his excess weight
so that he can
attack more quickly?
A dangerous gamble.
Tell me, Your Majesty.
Would you say that I am weak?
I know you haven't been
fighting me seriously today.
You're at ease and have
pulled back on every attack.
Am I truly that feeble to you?
Just tell me, I'd much rather
die knowing the truth.
[AINS]
To be honest, in this duel,
I've made all sorts
of magic items off-limits
and prohibited myself
from relying on
many of my normal abilities.
[WARRIOR KING]
Is that because
you'd win in an
instant, otherwise?
[AINS]
Yes, but don't feel too bad.
If you're the toughest
in the Empire,
then I'm most likely one of
the strongest in the world.
That's understandable.
It's been fun--
motivational, too--
knowing that there's always
someone stronger out there.
[AINS]
I can appreciate that sentiment.
[MOMONGA]
Touch.
Hear me, Sorcerer King
Ains Ooal Gown!
I would like to
witness true power!
No matter how briefly.
I want to feel it at its peak!
So, please show me the
extent of what you can do!
[AINS]
Very well!
I'd be happy to demonstrate
the pinnacle of strength!
High Tiered Physical
Nullification, release.
[yells]
[WARRIOR KING yells]
[panting]
[AINS]
Activate.
[CROWD gasps]
[AINS]
People of the Empire!
I am currently
forming an institution
for supporting adventurers.
Many are tasked with surviving
on their abilities alone,
and I believe that training
and cultivating them
will benefit my kingdom greatly!
But do not fear, I don't plan
to use these adventurers
as pawns of war.
As you have seen,
my offensive capabilities
leave nothing to be desired.
What I seek are people who want
to go on true adventures!
If you dream about discovering
the unknown, join me!
[AINS] Your endeavors will be
backed by my unimaginable power,
which I shall demonstrate here.
Death is the end,
but I can overcome it!
Behold!
[WARRIOR KING groans]
[AINS] Normally only
high-ranking priests
can use Resurrection
magic. But for me?
This is child's play!
Come to my kingdom and know
an adventure like none other!
[silence]
[AINS]
Fly.
Apologies about before.
As expected of Master Gown.
You defeated the strongest
warrior in the Empire.
That was quite
an impressive feat.
[AINS]
It was a good fight.
Either of us could have won,
but luck was on my side.
With that, I shall
take my leave.
[JIRCNIV]
One moment! I have a request!
Sorcerer King.
I pledge my full support to you.
Therefore, the Baharuth Empire
shall gladly become
your vassal state!
What?
Huh?
Seriously?
--Think this through!
--[NIMBLE] Are you sure, sir?
[AINS] There is much to consider
in becoming a vassal state.
[MOMONGA]
Like, what even is that?
[AINS] I'm afraid I can't offer
a response immediately,
so if I could at least get
that in writing from you.
Of course!
If that's what you want,
I'll send something right away!
[AINS]
Perfect. Draw up the document
explaining the Empire's proposed
relationship to my kingdom
and I shall respond accordingly.
Your Highness.
Know why I made the decision?
I hate to admit it, but his
cunning surpasses my own.
He's seen through our plans,
so we can't win anymore.
More importantly, why the hell
did he outright reject
my offer to become
a vassal state?
He shouldn't have any
reason to refuse me.
It must have been something that
went against his original plans.
Perhaps he's plotting to conduct
a terrible experiment on us!
Or perhaps, it has to
do with the adventurers
that he tried to recruit!
Maybe he's not
a plotting kinda guy?
There is no chance in hell!
But don't worry.
There are many types
of vassal states.
I'll do everything
I can to retain
some level of sovereignty.
Your Highness, aren't you
concerned about your own safety?
Well, of course.
But as grim as it sounds, the
best I can do is convince him
that I'm worth more
alive than dead.
I hope that's enough to save me.
I might be the unluckiest man
in the world right now.
Can you believe it?