[QUAGOA cackling]
[DWARVEN SOLDIER 406A]
What's going on? Still no news?
Can anyone give us a detailed
report on the situation?
[PLATOON LEADER 406A]
General! There are Quagoa
trying to invade our
stronghold as we speak!
We have magic defense items
installed to prevent this!
There's no way there's
that many of them!
Shut the gates immediately!
There are still soldiers
fighting, though!
Don't question me!
The citizens in Feo Jera
take priority!
[PLATOON LEADER 406A]
Close the gates!
[DWARVEN SOLDIERS yelling]
Don't let any of them in!
Spearmen! Get to the front!
Magicians, use lightning!
Thunder Ball!
[QUAGOA screaming]
[DWARVEN MAGICIANS]
Thunder Spear, go!
[QUAGOA scream]
[DWARVEN GENERAL]
Hurry! Lock it!
[PLATOON LEADER 406A] That
should hold them off for now!
The Quagoa will have a hard
time chomping through that!
Personally, sir, if I were you,
I'd consider deserting Feo Jera.
So, you're on the
same page as me.
[DWARVEN MESSENGER 406A]
Message! Message incoming!
General! This is urgent!
An undead entity appeared
at the surface entryway!
He wishes to speak to us
about the Quagoa!
[BOTH]
What did you say?
You won't believe it.
They were able to get
a Quagoa to talk.
Nabbed him in Feo Raidho.
Apparently, the Quagoa
figured out a way
to get across the Great Chasm,
so this party rushed
over to warn us.
[AINS]
Allow me to introduce myself.
I am Sorcerer King
Ains Ooal Gown.
[DWARVEN GENERAL] I-I'm head
general of the dwarven army!
[AINS] What an honor that
someone so prestigious
has come to welcome me.
I assume that means the Quagoa
have been giving you trouble?
Ah. Very astute.
You were able to tell so much
from the fact that
I came to greet you?
[AINS] The situation
is rather apparent.
It seems that the
Sorcerer King's aware
of our current predicament.
It's looking dire.
It's taking up
all of our resources
to hold off the Quagoa attacks.
And since we have
no additional forces,
we're considering
abandoning the city.
[AINS]
I'm here to offer assistance.
I'm trying to establish friendly
relations with your kingdom,
I would hate to
see it get destroyed.
Please consider
accepting my help.
Very well, but I must
speak with my supervisors,
the Regency Council.
[AINS] If you have time
to spare, I can wait.
However, I'm sure you've
heard the old saying
"a congress often dances
but does not move forward."
One moment, please.
What's our move, sir?
Come, Sorcerer King.
Let's discuss these details.
Your strength could
be a great help.
[YOHZ] So much for the Great
Chasm being impenetrable, huh?
Bet they're panicking.
Once we work our way around
that, we're pretty much in.
Those rare minerals
are as good as ours!
We will return victorious,
and Lord Riyuro will
be quite pleased.
Quickly. Go report to the
main force behind us.
Tell them we secured
the invasion route.
I'm on it, sir!
Are they conceding?
Let's butcher them. You ready?
No mercy! C'mere,
you little shrimps!
It's time to die!
[screams]
[DEATH KNIGHT 406A shrieks]
Crap! What was that?
Did the dwarves have
a counterattack planned?
I doubt it!
They're never gone
on the offensive!
[BOTH gasp]
[YOHZ]
What the hell?
[QUAGOA scream]
What am I looking at?
Giant dwarves?
[groaning]
[gasps] Cut the bridge!
[YOHZ yells]
[QUAGOA screaming]
[QUAGOA 406C]
Lord Yohz!
Those cowards, I think
they used golems!
Used what?
It's a type of monster.
Those damn dwarves must
have tamed 'em somehow.
But the golems shouldn't
be able to climb
their way back up, at least.
Change of plans, men!
Let's fall back!
We'll notify Lord Riyuro!
[DWARVEN GENERAL]
We have no king
and are run by
the Regency Council.
Every decision is made by them.
[AINS]
I see.
If you don't mind waiting here,
I'll just be a just few moments.
[AINS]
Of course-- What?
[gasps] Pardon me, Your Majesty,
is something the matter?
[AINS] Forgive me.
It's a personal issue.
Nothing to concern
yourself with.
[DWARVEN GENERAL]
Then if you'll excuse me,
I'll go speak with the
Regency Council immediately.
[AINS] It seems that the
two Death Knights I created
have been eliminated, somehow.
[GROUP gasps]
[MOMONGA] They both died
at the same time, too.
If it was the work
of a single opponent,
they must be at least level 45.
Have I finally found a player?
That would explain
how they dispatched
those Death Knights so quickly.
Maybe we're dealing
with the same culprit
that brainwashed Shalltear.
Thanks for your
patience, everyone.
They're ready for you.
Please follow me.
[AINS]
Mm.
[DWARVEN CHIEF OF STAFF]
His Majesty, the Sorcerer King,
has arrived!
[AINS] Greetings, esteemed
members of the Regency Council.
I am Ains Ooal Gown.
It's good of you
to come, You Majesty!
What a pleasure to meet you!
Please have a seat.
We have much to
discuss with you, sir.
Before we start, let us express
our sincerest gratitude
for your aid.
If it weren't for you,
our kingdom would have fallen
to the Quagoa by now.
[AINS] Everyone needs
help from time to time.
The general has already given us
a briefing on your goal.
You've come to establish
a friendly relationship
with our kingdom.
Is that more or less true?
[AINS]
Yes. I've heard that vegetables
are hard to obtain here,
so I can provide those.
And if liquor is
something of interest,
I can bring you plenty
from the human countries.
[ALL gasp]
Well. This all sounds nice,
but we don't have much to offer.
What did you want in exchange?
[AINS]
I desire ore.
My kingdom has little in
the way of natural deposits.
I see now.
[AINS] I would also like to
acquire weapons and armor
crafted in your workshops.
I'm told dwarves
make the very best.
Your Majesty, you have
already provided us
an invaluable service,
for which we are grateful,
but this offer will
require some thought.
[AINS] Please take all
the time you need.
There's no rush.
Shall we speak of the Quagoa?
I believe I have repelled
their invasion for now?
Through my strength alone.
It's just as you say.
Until you arrived, we held them
off with one set of doors.
Had they been breached,
many dwarves would've
been killed there.
[AINS] However, the peace that
we have won for Feo Jera
is temperory, I fear.
[DWARVEN GENERAL] Yes,
now that they've found a way
to get past the Great Chasm,
we can expect that
they'll attack again.
[AINS] Then you should not
wait until things are too dire
to accept help. So?
Shall I lend you my strength?
With my kingdom's power,
we can easily prevent
any invasion for the
foreseeable future.
It goes without saying that this
would be very beneficial to us.
[AINS] Allow me to
take it a step further.
What if we could go to their
nest in... Feo Berkana, was it?
Then I could reclaim
the old dwarven capital
for your country.
You say that like
it's so easy!
With all due respect,
that's too dangerous!
It's ruled over by a Clan Lord.
He controls all eight
Quagoa factions!
We don't stand a chance,
even with you.
Not to mention the capital
is impossible to get to.
Three impasses would be awaiting
you in the trails ahead!
[HIGH PRIEST OF EARTH]
And even if you're able
to get through alive, there's
a terrifying frost dragon
that's settled in that area.
[AINS]
Hm. How intriguing.
One moment.
Do you really think that we
can reclaim our old capital?
[AINS]
Indeed.
[FORGEMASTER]
I find that hard to believe.
Why help us to that extent?
What exactly are you after?
Now, let us be respectful.
[FORGEMASTER] If a stranger
walks into a bar and pays off
your whole tab, you gotta wonder
what he's after, don't you?
[AINS]
Your suspicions are warranted.
But it's those sensibilities
that make you a desirable ally.
Despite their strength,
I have decided not to align
with the Quagoa, because
they are beasts at heart.
Furthermore, I recognize
the losing side
is always more grateful for
help than the winning party,
so this is a fine opportunity
to build our trust.
Tch.
[AINS] The second reason--
and I'll be frank with you all--
is that you have something
I desire in return.
There's the catch.
Then this is a
business transaction.
[AINS] Yes, though it may be
different than you expect.
I want to invite your
runesmiths to my kingdom.
[GROUP]
Huh?
What did you say?
So, you're here to
enslave our people?
[AINS] Why would I do that
to country I wish to have
diplomatic relations with?
I merely want to invite
your dwarven artisans
to practice their craft
in my land. It's that simple.
How about instead
if we gave your kingdom
the right to purchase items
before they were
sent off to market.
[AINS]
No.
The returns would not be high
enough to warrant such a deal.
I want to be the sole producer
of rune technology.
If you want our strength
to regain your capital,
this is what I am
asking for in return.
[AINS]
When can I expect a response?
We'll need until
tomorrow, Your Majesty.
Need I remind you, the Quagoa
are already attacking us?
Forgive my comrade here.
Can you please go wait in the
reception room, Your Majesty?
We will make our decision
as soon as possible.
[GROUP]
Hm...
[sighs] Just what
the hell was that?
I've never met a more
fearsome monster!
Man! I practically
pissed my britches!
[HIGH PRIEST OF EARTH]
The wickedness runs deep
in that fellow.
He has an army of darkness.
I dunno how comfortable I am
with giving them weapons.
There's no way he can drink
alcohol with a body like that!
We all know a guy who
can't throw one back
with the boys is suspicious.
[SECRETARY GENERAL]
That's for damn sure.
[GROUP chattering]
[DWARVEN GENERAL]
Gentlemen!
Our country's in crisis,
we have no other choice.
If we don't accept this help
right now, we'll be destroyed.
Only one man can save us.
And alas, that man's
the Sorcerer King.
[GOVERNOR OF CAVES AND MINES]
Your Majesty,
after some deliberation,
we have decided to accept
the terms you have set forth.
[AINS]
A wise choice.
Then I will lend you enough
soldiers to reclaim
the stronghold immediately
and keep the Quagoa at bay.
As for the runesmiths,
we have agreed to let them
join your kingdom,
as you have requested.
You may take them
when you're done here.
However, we would like to
send an investigation party in
at a later date. To ensure
they're being treated well.
I'm sure you understand.
Do you accept these terms?
[AINS]
By all means.
I'll welcome your investigators
into the Sorcerer Kingdom
when the time comes.
[MOMONGA] They most likely want
to make sure labor regulations
are being adhered to.
After seeing how
Herohero's work treated him,
I wouldn't wish that on anyone.
I'll make a work
environment so positive,
it'll knock their
dwarven socks off!
[AINS]
Then, let us act immediately.
[RUNESMITH 406A]
I'm here! Hey, Gon-boy!
All right. I'm ready
for that special thing
you promised me!
I'll gladly give it to you after
the Sorcerer King's speech.
Just sit and wait for now.
C'mon, don't tease me.
Just a sip before
he gets started? Please?
His Majesty has
the alcohol anyway.
That Gondo can be so stingy!
Never had booze
like that before!
I'm sure you know what I mean.
I don't like booze that much.
I didn't bother
tasting it, myself.
You gotta be joking with me!
Drinking's 80 percent of life!
How wasteful!
Ugh. Same crap, different day.
[yelps]
[RUNESMITHS gasp]
[RUNESMITH 406C]
An undead!
[RUNESMITH 406A]
Huh? A monster?
--[AINS] Silen--
--[SHALLTEAR] Be quiet!
My apologies, Lord Ains,
did you say something just now?
[AINS]
It's all right.
I am the Sorcerer King
Ains Ooal Gown.
I have journeyed
from a kingdom south
of the Azerlisia mountains,
beyond the Great Forest of Tob.
It's truly a delight
to make the acquaintance
of skilled runesmiths
such as yourselves.
Now, what I have to say
is extremely brief
and it will be a
straightforward request.
I want you to come to my
kingdom and develop innovative
enhancement technology
using your runecraft.
[ELDER 406A]
I have a question, sir.
For what reason do you
want rune technology?
Honestly speaking, it's an
artform that's on its way out,
even in this country.
[RUNESMITHS gasp]
[ELDER 406A] Wow.
What a beautiful black blade.
[RUNESMITH 406A]
Let me get a closer look!
[RUNESMITH 406C]
Pass it here!
--Back away!
--[RUNESMITHS yelp]
[AINS]
Be quiet! What a racket!
Please let me finish.
I'd like to know if
it's possible for you
to inscribe 20 runes on
a single sword, like this.
Frankly, I've never
heard of such a thing.
To my understanding,
the most that can be engraved
on a single piece is six.
But that was done
over 200 years ago.
It's just a record from
the golden age.
[RUNESMITHS gasp]
[AINS]
I see.
Then this must have been
made with technology
that has been since
lost, unfortunately.
[ELDER 406A]
You don't know where it's from?
[AINS]
I merely acquired this weapon,
I have no clue of its origin.
The ones who created it
are no longer of this world.
Then that is a terrible tragedy.
[AINS]
My wish is simple.
This precious knowledge has
been lost to the sands of time.
I want to revive this valuable
craft in the modern age!
In order to do so,
I need the expertise
of craftsmen such as you!
I would like to try!
[RUNESMITHS chattering]
[MOMONGA] They were more
enthusiastic than I expected.
The presentation
went over swimmingly!
Man, I just love this
feeling of accomplishment!
I would jump for joy
right now if I could.
That was amazing
work, Lord Ains!
You really inspired those
dwarves back there!
You're the only man in Nazarick
who could accomplish
such a thing!
[AINS]
It was nothing.
I only spoke the truth.
What's wrong, Gondo?
[GONDO] I suppose that means
the Regency Council agreed
to send all the runesmiths
to the Sorcerer Kingdom?
[AINS]
They have.
[GONDO]
I see.
My country doesn't have
a need for runes anymore.
They really gave
it up that easy?
[AINS]
Yes, Gondo. That's right.
But I'm different from them,
I see the potential
in your craft.
You may have been
discarded by your people,
but you will be
cherished in my kingdom.
That means this is far
from the end, right?
[GONDO] I thank you from
the bottom of my heart.
We will do our best
to live up to your
expectations, Your Majesty.
[AINS] Starting tomorrow, we
will be leaving for a few days.
[GONDO]
Where are you headed, sir?
[AINS]
We're going to reclaim
the royal capital
of your people.
[gasps]
[DWARVEN GENERAL]
Your Majesty!
We came to talk to you about
your guide to the royal capital.
He insisted on
escorting you himself.
[AINS]
Hm.
Listen, I gave it
a lot of thought.
I talked it over
with my companions.
I've decided to join you
as I know the quickest
route to the capital.
[AINS] Gondo, I can't have you
risking your life like this.
[GONDO] I'm well aware
of the dangers, sir.
[clears throat]
[whispering] There's a treasury
there that includes a manual
of rune technology passed
down in the royal family.
I want to recover it
no matter the cost.
[AINS] Are you asking me to be
accessory to your pilfering?
Is that not a dwarven treasure?
[GONDO] Please, if a country
doesn't care if it loses
precious knowledge like that,
does it really need a book
about its secrets?
[AINS] I have a feeling I will
have a sudden bout of blindness
at what happens to be your
most opportune moment.
[gasps]
[AINS] Gondo, I shall
accept your guidance.
Outgoing party! Open 'em up!
[GONDO gasps]
[SHALLTEAR] Seems like
the Death Knights really put
these filthy beasts
in their place.
[AINS]
As one can expect.
--Mass Fly.
--[GONDO] Whoa!
[gasps] The bridge!
What happened here?
The Great Chasm is perilous
enough to cross on its own!
[AINS] I assume this is
the work of the Quagoa?
No, that can't be.
An opponent strong enough
to slay a Death Knight
would have no reason
to take out a bridge.
[AINS]
Shalltear, allow me to brief you
on some details while
we have the chance.
Pen and paper ready, My Lord!
[AINS clears throat]
We're about to go into
an extremely dangerous place.
I feel the need to
preemptively warn you,
there is a formidable foe
out there who was able
to best two of my Death Knights.
I shall do everything in
my power to defeat them!
[AINS] No, that is absolutely
not what you should do.
I'm afraid I don't understand.
[AINS] You must consider
what the enemy's
likely course
of action would be.
What our opponent wants
most is information--
a gauge on our strength.
[gasps]
[AINS] They will likely send in
a disposable strike team
to measure our capabilities.
Find something interesting
down there, kiddo?
That what I think it is?
Um. Pardon, Lord Ains.
[AINS]
Shh.
[AINS] As I was saying,
that's what I would do
against someone like that.
In fact, that's what my
comrades would've done, too.
You're sharing the wisdom of
the Supreme Beings with me?
[AINS] Shalltear, no matter
what, you must keep thinking.
Keep thinking. Keep
thinking. Keep thinking.
[AINS] Aura, what were
you trying to say?
It was nothing, sir! I'm sorry!
[AINS]
Mm. Very well.
Then, we should move forward
while preparing ourselves
for the possibility
of an enemy ambush.
[GONDO] There are still
two more dangerous areas!
The second one's a doozy.
[GONDO] A sea of lava with a
magical beast that--oh, well.
Alas, that's not all!
There's the labyrinth
of death, too!
It's a cave with
countless branching paths
where poisonous gas is
emitted from every direction.
Breathing it in
could result in death!
Gaseous or no, undead
beings aren't phased
by such inconveniences.
[AINS] Hence, we shall protect
the two of you with magic.
[AINS]
Breath of Titania.
[AINS] We'll be able to take
the quickest route through
using this.
Incredible!
[AURA]
Easy-peasy!
[AINS] Indeed. We'll reach
the royal capital soon.
Ready to hear
the rest of the plan?
[BOTH]
Yes!
[AINS] The two of you
will deal with the Quagoa.
If they submit to us, fine.
If they resist, do not hesitate
to show them the
power of Nazarick!
Oh, heck yeah!
As you wish, My Lord!
[AINS] I'll take care
of the dragon, myself.
[AINS]
A frost element, huh?
I've heard that there are quite
a few living frost dragons
that make their nests
on the other side
of the Azerlisia mountains.
There could be
hundreds up there.
[AINS] Ninya. You wouldn't
happen to know
the name of the dragon
with the power over nature?
[NINYA]
Huh?
Sorry. No idea.
[AINS] She said she
would find out the truth
once we made it back to town.
A shame she died.