[knocking]
[REP OF INTERNAL AFFAIRS]
Your Highness.
I'm sorry for intruding
so late at night.
Since my captor
is here to see me,
I can only assume what happened.
Our kingdom has fallen.
The day is lost.
So it seems. Soon, at least.
[RAMPOSA III]
Hm?
[REP OF INTERNAL AFFAIRS]
In short, we've lost all contact
with the royal army, and none
of the messengers we've sent
to the battlefield
have returned.
Prince Zanac's whereabouts
are also unknown.
My poor, foolish boy.
You had to follow your brother.
To think that both of my sons
would go before me.
I am relieving everyone
in the castle
of their positions immediately.
If they hurry, they might
still have a chance to escape
under the veil of night.
Understood, My Lord.
That includes you.
[gasps] Your Majesty.
I will stay here and
meet our conqueror,
as the last king
of this fallen kingdom.
[BABY crying]
I worry that the children
are making too much racket.
You can never be too careful.
If we offend the emissary,
it could mean our death.
I'm bored!
How long do we have to wait
for these guys to show up?
We got our families and
everyone from the Eight Fingers
ready to ship out.
Does this Sorcerer guy
care if we're all here?
Watch it, Cocco Doll!
Uh-- Sorry, I mean...
"His Majesty"!
You're our colleague.
We must introduce you to
the Sorcerer King's emissary.
[COCCO DOLL] Hey, don't
get me wrong, I'm grateful.
I was just venting a little!
That aside, I still don't
get why you bothered
to break someone
like me outta prison!
What are you trying to imply?
I'm a has-been. I lost all
my power and connections,
so it just seems
like you're being
awfully generous to me.
What's your objective exactly?
Why would you say
such a thing, Ampetif?
You're one of us!
Of course we'll help you!
We're in this together, always!
Uh-- Huh?
Okay, no, this is weird.
Something's up.
You're not an
imposter, are you?
You're the same old Hilma?
If you're a monster
wearing her skin,
just come out and
say it already!
You really think I've
changed that much?
Yeah! And you're all so thin!
Did you get on some
weird diet together?
You don't look the same
or act the same!
It'd make more sense if you
were a bunch of skin-stealers!
What can I say?
It shows how much
we've been through.
Been through what exactly?
[ALL gasp]
We'll be destroying
the royal capital soon,
so I've come to bring
all of you to safety.
I've been told you have 1,000
people that are coming with you?
Bring them here and
we'll depart immediately.
Yes, ma'am.
Come, Shadow Demon.
Pardon me.
If you could spare a moment,
while we're waiting on them,
there's someone I believe
we should introduce you to.
That won't be necessary.
Rather, we should gather
your luggage first.
[GROUP]
Huh?
[SHALLTEAR]
You will stay here
until we can transport
you to a proper home.
I'll return to check
on you in a few days,
but you should have
adequate food and supplies
to last till then.
You're one of the
executives, correct?
Uh, yes!
There something
you require of me?
You need to be taken to
Kyouhukou, as the others were.
Huh?
--[yelps] Hey! Ow!
--[SHALLTEAR] Gate!
But I don't want to go!
Help! No!
[SHALLTEAR]
Yes, yes. Come along now.
Why are you all
making that face?
C'mon, say something!
Help!
There's nothing we could have
done to save the poor man.
Don't say it like that.
He will survive, after all.
It's better to think of it
as a rite of passage.
It will bring us
closer in the end.
Yes, you're right.
We thank you for your mercy,
great Sorcerer King.
[AINS]
Delay Teleportation.
Body of Effulgent Beryl.
Life Essence.
Mana Essence.
[AINS]
Good. Now I need only wait.
[ALBEDO] If the enemy
wants to make a move,
this will be their last chance.
[ALBEDO]
I'll proceed as planned.
[AINS] Yes, but be careful
not to kill him.
Remember, our goal
is to collect information.
[ALBEDO]
Of course. But what about you?
[AINS]
There's no need to worry.
I will play my part
to perfection.
You need only do the same.
[ALBEDO]
Always.
Ah, excuse me, I mean,
as you wish, Lord Ains.
[AINS]
Chain Dragon Lightning, huh?
[ALBEDO]
How insolent! State your name!
[cackles]
[gasps]
[AINS] Go, Albedo!
Don't let the enemy escape!
[ALBEDO]
Right!
[ALBEDO] I'd catch him easily
if I could use my War Bicorn.
Not very subtle, are you?
Do you really think I don't
notice that you're leading me
away from Lord Ains?
He won't fall so easily.
But how far does he plan to go?
Perhaps I was the
target all along.
[ALBEDO]
Revealing your power to me?
Be my guest!
[ALBEDO] Those aren't
even magic projectiles.
Are you just testing my armor?
Well, I certainly know
what's coming next.
Physical projectiles don't work,
so you'll try hitting me
with a spell.
Let's see it, then.
[ALBEDO]
No damage.
Perhaps it's not attack magic,
but instant death magic?
Did you expect such low-tier
magic to work on me?
I find that offensive!
[ALBEDO] He's so weak!
It's like punching tofu!
[ALBEDO] What a boorish
little goon you are,
and cowardly as well!
I'll sever your limbs
and grind you with my boot
till you offer Lord Ains
a proper apology
for your insolence.
[AZUTH] Just what I'd expect
from a genocidal butcher.
[ALBEDO] Oh, and here I was
thinking you were some savage,
incapable of human speech!
Well, the people of this kingdom
might as well be animals,
seeing how foolish
and weak they are.
[AZUTH]
Your poison tongue is unbecoming
of a prime minister, Albedo.
Your invasion was
never justified.
You're the savages, using any
excuse to slaughter people.
No. You're worse than that.
You're monsters.
So call my methods
cowardly all you want.
This is a battle
against pure evil.
[ALBEDO]
Let him talk.
Maybe the fool will slip up
and reveal something.
[AINS]
Nothing is happening.
How odd. Surely he's
not working alone.
[AINS]
Explode Mine!
I may be standing in the open,
but I'm hardly defenseless.
[AINS]
Life Essence.
It seems he has
a lot of HP left.
As for his MP, none at all.
A pure warrior class, then.
[AINS laughs] Thought you
were clever, did you?
Indeed, skeletons are weak
against blunt attacks,
but I've taken special
care to address that.
Don't take me for a fool!
So, you can put
your hammer away.
No weapon of the sort
will work on me!
[RIKU]
World Isolation Barrier.
[AINS]
Wait a minute.
His HP dropped when
he used that technique.
[AINS] I'll forgive you
for the surprise attack.
I believe you know who I am,
but allow me to introduce
myself all the same.
I am the Sorcerer King,
Ains Ooal Gown.
Now, your turn.
Will you grace me
with your name as well?
[RIKU]
Riku Aganeia.
[AINS] Hm. I can't say
I've heard of you.
Though that platinum armor
of yours does make me wonder.
There was a nameless warrior
among the Thirteen Heroes
that was known for the
platinum armor he wore.
Could it be that I'm
dealing with a celebrity?
At any rate, a pleasure
to meet you, Riku Aganeia.
So, may I call you Riku?
[RIKU]
You may not.
[AINS]
Forgive me for being informal.
Sir Aganeia it is, then.
Unless you object
to that as well.
[RIKU]
No, that's fine.
[AINS]
In that case,
Sir Aganeia, I have
a proposal for you.
Why don't you become
my subordinate?
[RIKU]
I refuse.
[AINS]
You won't even consider it?
The strong are valued
in my kingdom, you know.
In fact, if you joined me,
I could easily be persuaded
to stop my attack on Re-Estize.
A talented warrior like yourself
is worth more than any land.
Hm. If he doesn't care,
perhaps he isn't from Re-Estize.
So much for diplomacy,
I suppose.
[RIKU]
Cloak of Light.
[AINS]
His HP went down again.
Greater Teleportation.
[AINS]
My magic failed.
I see.
This must be the barrier
he cast earlier.
It doesn't seem to be magic
or a normal skill.
It blocks teleportation.
And physical objects, too.
Body of Effulgent Beryl!
[AINS grunts]
Knock-back?
[AINS] Another attack
that reduced his HP.
I told you blunt damage
would not harm me.
Are you really that stubborn?
[RIKU] Keep talking if you must,
but your fate is sealed.
You will die within
this barrier, by my hand.
[AINS]
Twin Magic. Obsidian Sword.
What?
Wall of Skeleton!
[AINS]
Blasting Staff!
Grasp Heart!
No good?
[AINS]
I need to move!
Greater Teleportation!
Body of Effulgent Beryl!
It's not just the weapons.
It looks like he's controlling
the armor remotely, too.
[AINS]
Call Greater Thunder!
Are you surprised?
While this Blasting Staff
doesn't have much physical
attack power, it more
than makes up for it
with its strong
knock-back effect.
Convenient for a magic
caster such as myself,
since I like to create distance
between me and my enemies.
Summon Undead Tenth-Tier!
Doom Lord.
[AINS] Now, show me the full
extent of your strength!
[AINS]
Seems to be about level 90.
A tank that specializes
in hand-to-hand combat.
His weapons have HP, too.
And I noticed something
when I knocked him back.
The swords were sent
flying with him.
That would imply that
those floating weapons
are a part of his
body in some way.
I must assume that he's
controlling them and the armor
from another location.
I think that's all the
information my Doom Lord
can draw out.
Time to finish things up.
Here as well.
[AINS]
Summon Undead Tenth-Tier!
Elemental Skull!
Unlike the Doom Lord, this
summon specializes in magic,
commanding the power of
the four elemental spirits.
I'm sure you're weak to
at least one of those elements,
so now it's time
to find out which.
Or, we can cease this charade,
now that we have a grasp
of each other's strengths.
Ah-- Wait! No!
I'm still talking!
[AINS]
Please! I beg of you!
Just a moment of your time!
I have no desire to
fight you to the death!
This all began when
Re-Estize stole provisions
intended as aid for
the Holy Kingdom!
I believe it's clear who
is at fault in this situation.
Unless you object to our
charity for some reason,
surely you don't think
we're wrong for taking action
after we were attacked.
[RIKU] The action you
took was excessive.
[AINS]
What would you have done?
What if it was your
food that was stolen?
Would you still think
that this thieving kingdom
would be worth protecting?
[RIKU] Those who possess power
must use it responsibly.
You cannot act solely
in your own self-interest.
That's why I will
protect this world,
or rather, why I
must protect it.
Absolute power is
the root of evil.
A sin I carry as well, but
I won't beg for forgiveness.
Rather I shall use it
to extinguish wickedness
from the world,
starting with you.
Now perish!
[ALBEDO]
Mind your filthy tongue!
You worm!
[ALBEDO] How dare you speak
to Lord Ains that way!
I'll make you suffer!
Get back here!
[AINS]
Albedo, stop! That's enough!
[ALBEDO]
My Lord.
[AINS]
Sir Aganeia.
Before you depart,
I will ask you once more.
Will you not serve me?
I will grant you
whatever you may wish!
The gates of
the Sorcerer Kingdom
will always be open to you.
Come visit me
whenever you please!
[AINS]
A pity.
But with that, our job is done.
Good work.
[ALBEDO]
Our enemy is still unknown.
I worry that there
may be eyes upon us.
We should return
to Nazarick immediately.
[AINS]
A fine idea. Let's depart.
[RIKU]
I hope you weren't waiting long.
[AZUTH]
Hey, Tsa!
[RIKU] It seems you survived
your encounter with that demon.
Yeah, but I couldn't
even hit her.
Best I could do was
keep her at a distance.
Used every weapon at my disposal
and she shrugged 'em off,
one after another.
I'm sorry.
Wish I could've
held her off a bit.
But that aside, how'd you fare
against the Sorcerer King?
[RIKU]
Poorly, to be quite honest.
Guess that's it, then.
For the kingdom, at least.
[RIKU]
Forgive me.
You put your life at risk,
and I couldn't finish the job.
Don't blame yourself for this.
I'm the one who couldn't
buy you enough time, right?
[RIKU]
No, you did your part well.
Given your opponent,
I could scarcely expect more.
To be frank, time
wasn't the issue.
I failed to defeat the
Sorcerer King because he was
much stronger than
I had anticipated.
Still, it's strange.
The World Isolation Barrier
worked perfectly against
the Sorcerer King, but Albedo
seemed to break through it
quite easily when
she came to his aid.
The space was isolated
from the outside world.
The only way she could
have made it through
was if she used wild magic
or possessed a world item.
She appears to be subservient
to the Sorcerer King,
but perhaps she's the "player"
and he's the "NPC."
It could be a method to
protect herself from enemies.
Pretending to be
second-in-command
would have a few advantages.
And she did seem
suspiciously powerful.
Or perhaps the Sorcerer King
has more than one world item.
Though that would mean that he
chose not to bring it with him
to the battlefield
for some reason.
So, he's strong,
but what do you think
our odds are for next time?
Even if we weren't
able to pull this off,
you must've figured
something out, right?
Y'think I--or rather,
y'think my suit could win?
[RIKU] Don't take this
the wrong way, Azuth,
but you wouldn't stand a chance.
Yet as you said,
I know his power now,
and that also means
I know its limits.
While I can't hope to
defeat him in a single blow,
I should be able to win,
provided he doesn't have
any allies with him.
Well, hey! Not bad!
Though I'd expect nothing less.
You are the world's
strongest dragon lord.
[RIKU] I do my best, but I'm
sure there are many beings
out there stronger than me.
Thankfully, my skill
set is well suited
to beating the Sorcerer King.
Oh! Before I forget.
When he asked for my name,
I said it was "Riku Aganeia."
Good to remember that,
in case it comes up.
I'll write it down
when I get the chance.
Does that name have
a special meaning?
[RIKU]
Not at all.
I didn't plan ahead,
and it was the first thing
that came to mind.
Now that I think about it,
I hope no one is actually
named that, or they're about
to have a very bad time.
That should keep
the Sorcerer King busy,
trying to hunt down someone
who doesn't even exist.
[RIKU]
Not only him, his Prime Minister
certainly seems like the
type to hold a grudge.
I could not have accomplished
what I did today
without your help,
and I can't defeat
these evil "players" on my own.
So please take care of
yourself until next time.
Azuth has been agreeable
thus far, but I worry.
Perhaps it would be better
to kill him and give his armor
to a more capable
and obedient ally.
Riku. I already have
blood on my hands.
No turning back.
I could blame his death
on the Sorcerer King,
but if someone resurrected him,
then they would
find out the truth.
I can't afford to do
anything I'll regret.
[AINS]
Outstanding work, Albedo.
Pandora's Actor.
[BOTH]
Thank you.
[PANDORA'S ACTOR]
Truly, I am undeserving
of such praise, My Lord!
[AINS] I observed your battle,
but I'd like to hear
your impression of
this "Riku Aganeia,"
since you interacted
with him directly.
His words, his emotions,
all that you could draw out
of this man, everything the
mirror could not convey.
Reveal it to me.