[KORO-SENSEI laughs]
[KORO-SENSEI] All right, people,
let's get started, shall we?
Whoever feels ready,
come get some!
[CLASS screams]
[KORO-SENSEI] I'm afraid
you've got miles to go
before you're heroes.
[OKAJIMA]
We're doing our best!
[KORO-SENSEI]
And denied again!
[NAKAMURA]
He's too friggin' quick!
Ugh. Face it, people:
We're Level One.
We got a snowball's
chance in hell.
I know, and all we got for
weapons are these wooden sticks.
Speak for yourself,
mine's made of plastic.
[GOOD BOYS &amp; GIRLS]
Mightiest Warrior in the Land!
[KORO-SENSEI]
That's unhygienic!
Poor Isogai has it the worst.
Granted, the suit of armor
makes him look heroic.
But only from the front side.
[GOOD BOYS &amp; GIRLS]
It's his butt!
It was all my family could do
to scrounge up
the cash for half.
[MAEHARA]
What respectable retail chain
even sells them like that?
Anyway, point being:
None of us are ready.
[SUGINO]
I don't get it.
Why choose the nobodies
in E-class for this?
[NAGISA]
Kunugigaoka School of Magic,
where students from
all over the world
come to forge themselves
into heroes.
Complete with a backwoods
satellite campus for kids
who don't make the cut.
That's where E-class meets,
and where we share a secret
no one else in the
entire school knows.
This year, for some reason,
our teacher just so
happens to be...
...the Big Bad!
Huh. So he really does exist.
[NAGISA]
Koro-Q!
So I'll just come
right out and say it.
I'm gonna need you young people
to kill this thing for us.
[KORO-SENSEI]
Hiddy-ho, class!
I'm the Big Bad Demon King,
or as of today, your teacher.
[CLASS]
Yeah, no.
Right, so first off,
know that he's fast,
even by Demon King standards.
[CLASS]
Is that actually a thing?
But how are we supposed
to take him on?
And why us in the first place?
[KARASUMA] Because apparently
there's only one way
to land an attack on him,
and I have it on good authority
that your bugs are the key.
[CLASS]
Huh?
[KORO-SENSEI] A bug is whatever
sets you apart from the herd.
Those little idiosyncrasies
that make you who you are.
Take Isogai for example.
His inability to buy the
back half of a suit of armor
is, in fact, a bug.
You mean it's not just because
my family's dirt poor?
[KORO-SENSEI]
Money,
or rather the lack
thereof in your case,
should not allow you to buy
only half a suit of armor.
So is me only being equipped
with plumbing
hardware a bug, too?
Or how my magic only
attracts actual bugs?
[KORO-SENSEI]
You bet'cha.
Is it the same for my cup size?
And me not being able to
throw away dirty magazines?
[KORO-SENSEI] No, those
are definitely not bugs.
Think of him as a final boss.
If there's any hope
of him being defeated,
it's in what makes
you children unique.
[CLASS]
Oh.
[KORO-SENSEI] Your government
and I came to an understanding.
They will allow me
to teach E-class,
and in return, I train
you all to beat me.
[CLASS]
Why?!
[KORO-SENSEI]
An astute question to be sure.
The simple answer?
It's lonely at the top.
I'm anxious to know
what it feels like
to take on an equal in battle,
or, more succinctly...
...I want to become stronger!
We all caught the
reference, right?
[CLASS]
He's really into this.
Mr. K-- Uh. Commander?
Is there any sort of
time limit on this?
I'm not sure that I--
Got it. So it depends
on our ratings. Right.
[NAGISA] What do you call an
un-killable Demon King teacher?
Koro-sensei!
[NAGISA]
Oh. Never mind.
Guess that works. Sure. Why not?
Koro-sensei and the E-class.
Things are gonna get weird.
[KAEDE]
Koro- Q!
[KUNUDON] Talk! Don't try
to fight it! Fess up!
Look, if you want a sibling,
go to bed for Christ sakes.
You're spoiling the mood!
[KUNUDON screams]
[NAKAMURA]
Koro-Q!
[GOOD BOYS &amp; GIRLS]
Tell us, Mr. Principal Asano!
[ASANO]
Good morning, students.
This is, of course,
your principal speaking.
Quite a few desperate queries
crowding my inbox today
from those among you
less well adjusted.
Hm. Let's address
some concerns, shall we?
Here's one from a lost
soul who calls himself
"Longing for Two-D Life."
"I study day and night with
every fiber of my being,
but so far, the results
have been mixed."
Is it possible I'm
pushing myself too hard?"
Hm. Oh, Takebayashi.
Please. "Every fiber of
your being," you say?
I think not.
Do you forego sleep?
Meals? Excretory functions?
Are you coughing up blood?
Do you feel the icy fingers
of death creeping up your spine
as you study those books?
If not, then I highly
recommend you stop whining
and push harder.
[HINANO]
Koro-Q!
[KORO-SENSEI]
Today you'll be taking on
your nasty arch nemeses: Slimes.
Kind of a sad arch nemesis, huh?
Well, we are pretty weak.
[KORO-SENSEI] That's precisely
the negative mindset
I'm trying to condition you
out of with this exercise.
You're only as weak as you
imagine yourself to be.
Break that spell,
and the sky's the limit.
The slimes in these parts
are on the warpath,
and rather full of
themselves, to be frank.
Teach them some humility.
Whoa! Behind you!
Hey, lookie here!
[SLIME KUNUDON C]
E-class must be feelin' brave!
I don't remember anybody
givin' you kids permission
to be on our turf!
[CLASS]
Wow. Attitude much?
[SLIME KUNUDON B]
Uh? Uh-oh. It's the Demon King!
[SLIME KUNUDON A]
Why's he slumming on this level?
[SLIME KUNUDON C]
Seriously!
Wait, I get it. Those
humans are his sacrifice.
[SLIME KUNUDON C chuckles]
Your Highness! Nice to see you!
To what do we owe the pleasure
of your, uh, honorable presence?
Please accept this small
token of our esteem!
[KORO-SENSEI]
The only sacrifice here today
is you pitiful creatures.
[SLIME KUNUDONS] Hold on a
second. How is that even fair?
[CLASS yelling]
[SLIME KUNUDONS]
Charge!
[GIRLS whimper]
Leave them be!
[GIRLS]
What a man!
He's half naked!
I've got this!
[GIRLS]
He's like a prince!
Whatever. Get a load of me!
[GIRLS]
That's disgusting!
What'd I do wrong?!
--[thudding]
--[OKAJIMA yelping]
Hey, Koro-sensei.
I'm ready to give it a try!
[chuckles]
[KORO-SENSEI]
Show me that bloodlust.
[NAGISA] We've been labeled
misfits and cast aside,
but for once, our
outlook is positive.
If we just apply ourselves,
things will change.
[CLASS]
Nagisa? Huh?
[NAGISA yells
[CLASS]
What the hell?
[KORO-SENSEI] It would appear
that Nagisa's particular bug
is marked by random
stat changes.
[NAGISA] This must be what
God-mode feels like!
Time to hit these slimes
with everything I've got.
Achievement unlocked!
Fire!
[SLIME KUNUDON ARMY screams]
Yes! I am now
conqueror of slime!
[CLASS]
What kind of magic was that?!
Nagisa's leading by example
to help us crush our foes!
Yeah, with our powers combined,
they'll be toast!
[CLASS yells]
[chuckles]
[SLIME KUNUDON A]
Hey! Who do you think you are?!
[SLIME KUNUDON B]
Just kidding! Uncle! Uncle!
[SLIME KUNUDON C]
We're sorry!
We're not worthy
to lick your boots!
[SLIME KUNUDONS]
But just so we're clear,
we totally let you win!
[CLASS laughing]
[KORO-SENSEI]
Nicely done.
I'd say the dark clouds
of your "misfit mindset"
have finally begun to part.
[NAGISA]
Um, sir.
I was just curious when
I'd change back to normal...
[KORO-SENSEI screams]
[NAGISA]
Okay...
[KORO-SENSEI]
Trust me, a sauna's the best way
to rid your body of toxins--
and that troublesome bug.
But I thought our
bugs were good!
[splashing]
I haven't changed even a little!
[KORO-SENSEI grunting]
[NAGISA]
How come you're shrinking?
[KORO-SENSEI]
To be continued.