[NAGISA]
Kunugigaoka School of Magic,
where students from
all over the world
come to forge themselves
into heroes.
We're E-class.
Outsiders. Underdogs.
And we share a secret no one
else in the school knows.
This year, our teacher
just so happens to be...
...the Demon King!
[KORO-SENSEI]
Alrighty. Take your best shot!
[NAGISA] Another day with the
one-and-only Koro-sensei.
Here goes nothin'!
[KORO-SENSEI]
Okay.
My goal, boys n' girls,
is to train a war party
capable of giving the Demon
King a run for his money.
To get started,
we need some heroes,
however, I'm sad to say
there doesn't seem to be
anyone here who
meets the criteria.
[CLASS gasps]
But there's Isogai!
[KORO-SENSEI] Granted,
between his leadership skills
and undeniable courage, he does
have a certain heroic streak.
There's just one problem.
In his case, the phrase
"heroic streak"
has an unfortunate
double meaning.
[CLASS]
Harsh!
Okay then, if Isogai
doesn't fit the bill,
then who do we have that does?
[KORO-SENSEI] Not to put too
fine a point on it, but moi!
[MAEHARA]
That defeats the purpose!
So what are we supposed to do?
Well, when the conversation
turns to mighty warriors,
three names never
fail to be brought up.
[KORO-SENSEI] How long have
you been standing there?
I recommend enlisting the
three of them to your ranks.
The first is said to
dwell in a northern cave
and call himself Karma,
a.k.a. The Red Devil.
Legend has it, his abilities
are way above average.
I've heard of that guy!
Yeah, he's supposed to be a
super-sadistic ranger type,
I think!
Sorta hard to believe
we have a living legend
in our own backyard.
The second is Ritsu,
known as the Evolved Mage.
Dwelling in a northern cave,
her magic is rumored to
evolve on a daily basis.
Third is the Silver
Berserker, Itona.
The story goes that deep
within a northern cave--
Just how many northern
caves are there?!
[NAGISA]
Koro-Q!
[KUNUDON] Talk! Don't
try to fight it! Fess up!
Remember that birthday money
you asked me to keep safe?
Yeah, Mama treated herself
to the Korean spa!
[KUNUDON]
No!
[NAGISA]
Koro-Q!
[KORO-SENSEI]
Here we are, class:
The secret lair
of the Red Devil.
[MIMURA]
Secret, yeah.
[KORO-SENSEI]
Okie-dokie!
Hand these out if you would,
please. One each.
What are these, boat anchors?
[KORO-SENSEI] The strategy
guide for this dungeon.
Everything you need to know
compiled into one
handy-dandy manual:
Maps, monsters, treasure
chests, save points--
you name it,
I've got you covered!
[GOOD BOYS &amp; GIRLS] No
self-respecting dungeon raider
should be without one!
[KORO-SENSEI laughing]
[KORO-SENSEI] Isn't being on the
attack side of things exciting?
[MAEHARA]
So exciting.
[KORO-SENSEI]
The sealed portion of the book
deals with more adult monsters.
[OKAJIMA, MAEHARA, SUGINO] We
talkin' parental advisory stuff?
[KORO-SENSEI]
And of course the final page
lays out details regarding
the dungeon boss himself.
[MAEHARA]
What does "irregularities
in his luck trait" mean?
[KAEDE]
I was about to ask.
Heh. All bark and no bite, huh?
You could live a bazillion years
and not get close to beating me.
[KORO-SENSEI]
Ah, yes.
You see, when Karma thinks
opponents are beneath him...
[OPPONENTS chuckling]
That's right, fleabags!
Laugh it up while you can.
After that, go run
back to the shelter
and get yourselves euthanized!
[KORO-SENSEI] The effect on
his luck is rather negative.
[OPPONENTS laughing]
[KORO-SENSEI]
That's his bug.
When he acts cocky or
looks down on someone,
his luck takes an
astronomical plunge.
[CLASS]
Oh, I get it. Karma!
[KORO-SENSEI] A shame, really.
Oodles of potential.
He'd make a great warrior if not
for the disagreeable tendency
to lord his prowess over others.
[chuckles]
[KAEDE, NAGISA] Kinda like
you're doing right now,
you mean?!
[MAEHARA] Wow. This place
is crawling with booby traps.
[NAKAMURA]
Dude must be a total sadist.
Not that his
handiwork's gonna do much
to slow down Koro-sensei.
[KORO-SENSEI]
A little poison ought'a dial up
the danger quotient a notch.
[NAKAMURA] We still have to walk
through those, you know!
[KORO-SENSEI] And these blasé
blades are simply screaming
for a much-needed
artistic makeover.
[FUWA, OKUDA, NAKAMURA, OKAJIMA]
We don't need that kinda danger!
[NAGISA] Questing through
a dungeon's a lot easier
with someone like Koro-sensei
blazing a trail out
ahead of you,
but where are the monsters?
[SUGINO]
Heads up! Monster incoming!
[OKAJIMA]
An adult one?
Dang it. Never mind. Huh?
Wait. They're in
the strategy guide.
Right, so apparently
these guys only smile
when they see
lower-level adventurers.
[OKAJIMA]
Ouch!
[MAEHARA]
That's obnoxious.
[gasps]
[MUSHROOM KUNUDONS]
Like moths to a flame!
[MUSHROOM KUNUDONS chuckle]
Holy crap! They're
all over the place!
Are we in trouble?
[KORO-SENSEI]
Not to worry, children.
Monsters can't attack the
Final Boss. I'll be fine!
[CLASS]
That's dumb!
[KORO-SENSEI]
Uh?
[MUSHROOM KUNUDONS gasp]
[NAGISA]
Karma!
[KORO-SENSEI] The boy
was incognito! Ingenious!
[HINANO]
He actually hurt him.
Am I wrong or does that
make him the first?
[KARMA] And here I
thought "Koro-sensei"
was a play on the Japanese
for "un-killable teacher."
Guess the teacher part
was true, at least.
Anyway.
Impressive bob-and-weave you
pulled there, 'fraidy cat.
Aw, c'mon. What's wrong?
Are you scared?
Do I intimidate you?
[KORO-SENSEI]
Imma need you to step off!
[CLASS]
Karma!
Oh, man, that is
one serious bug.
Worst luck ever!
Sure, but still, he did
land the first blow.
Good to know he isn't all hype.
[KORO-SENSEI grunting]
[KORO-SENSEI]
Go bald.
[MAEHARA]
Um, is he punching a wall?
People actually do that?
[NAKAMURA] Karma's smack-talk
seems to have really
touched a nerve.
Got a little careless
there for a second.
No disrespect, chief,
I'm just surprised the Demon
King's such a featherweight.
Well, well. Hey, Nagisa.
What's up? It's been a while.
[NAGISA, KAEDE, OKAJIMA gasp]
L-Long time no see.
Whoa, whoa. Say what?
Oh. We've known each
other since we were kids.
So, uh, how the hell're
you bottom-feeders
kickin' it with the Final Boss?
[OKAJIMA]
Damn! Sick burn on Nagisa!
[GOOD BOYS &amp; GIRLS]
And you!
Look, we, uh, want you
to join our war party.
You're the only
chance we've got.
I always knew you were amazing,
but that attack a minute ago?
Work with us and Koro-sensei's
as good as defeated.
[KARMA]
Hmm...
[CLASS]
He thinks we suck.
Come on. seriously?
Even if I did join you...
[CLASS]
Like, sincerely suck.
...I think we all
know it'd be my kill.
[KORO-SENSEI]
That's no-- Ah!
[KARMA]
Heh.
You're mine now.
[gasps]
[MUSHROOM KUNUDON A]
Eh?
My life is meaningless.
Where'd he run off to?
[KORO-SENSEI] Sorry.
It's this cave. I felt grimy.
Did you take a bath?!
[KORO-SENSEI]
No disrespect, but to be honest,
you were so slow and
that trap so tedious,
I thought, "why not make
the most of my time
and zip over to a hot springs
for a nice, soothing dip?"
Just the ticket, too.
Healed that nasty
wound up like magic.
[KARMA] You're not supposed to
bathe yourself in a hot spring!
[KARMA yells]
[KORO-SENSEI]
Zip. Snip.
Oh, really?
[KORO-SENSEI] You're strong,
Karma, I'll give you that.
Quick on your feet,
literally and figuratively.
Hey, quit tryin' to wash
my back, it's weird!
Creep thinks he can just--!
[KORO-SENSEI] The trouble
is you let those talents
go to your head.
If wielded in arrogance,
a blade will never touch me.
The Demon King isn't felled
by a single player,
but by a team of skilled
warriors working in tandem.
Camouflaging yourself was
an exceptionally clever move.
Why not shroud yourself in the
mantel of E-class next time?
[KARMA]
I see.
You want me to be part
of the group, too.
Fine.
Give me my clothes back and
I'll give it some thought.
All right, there we go.
Dammit I didn't agree to this!
I said I'd give it some thought!
[GIRLS] E-class proudly
welcomes our newest member!
[KARMA]
What is wrong with you people?!
And your banner looks
like a bad website!
And why the stupid dialog box?
[CLASS]
Hip-hip, hooray!
[NAGISA] And that's how
you drag the Red Devil
into being part of your clique.
Which brings us that
much closer to victory!
But I still haven't said yes!