[KIMURA]
Go us, am I right?
We've got the Red Devil.
And the Evolved Mage!
That's two legendary
warriors on our team!
Yeah, I gotta admit,
you're in pretty good hands
if you wanna kill the octopus.
You know, we've come this far,
so we might as well
recruit the third one.
[KORO-SENSEI] Bringing all
three legendary warriors
into the fold would increase
your odds of victory.
Trying to have a
conversation here!
[KORO-SENSEI]
You don't have to be mean.
I'm just trying to contribute.
It's kinda awkward when we're
talkin' about killin' you.
The third one's called
the Silver Berserker.
Sounds a little intense.
[KORO-SENSEI] I believe
his given name is Itona.
Ooo! Why don't we gather intel
on him for today's lesson?
[ITONA]
No need for that.
Victory's mine.
I've proven that I'm
stronger than this wall.
[CLASS] This guy's even
worse than the first two!
[SHIRO]
Apologies for startling you.
This is the prospective
new recruit
you were looking for, yes?
I bring him to you
new and improved.
Behold the next Demon King.
[KORO-SENSEI]
Uh! It's you!
[SHIRO]
We meet again, Koro-sen--
[KORO-SENSEI]
Yanagisawa!
[FUWA gasps]
Spoiler alert!
Fuwa.
[clears throat]
[SHIRO] I am Shiro a humble mage
sent by the Demon King's Army
to dispatch its leader.
Koro-sensei has an army?
[SHIRO] To think such
a fearsome creature
would stoop to
teaching outcasts.
What a tragic waste of
your considerable gifts.
In fact, it's caused
quite the scandal.
[KUNUDON]
Shocker!
Big Bad Beset by Big Bongos.
[KORO-SENSEI]
Boobies!
If you could see your way clear
to give me a teensy-weensy
raise, I'd be most grateful.
[KUNUDON]
Read all about it
under-the-radar
rendezvous with royalty!
[KORO-SENSEI]
Who is saying that?
Wow. Way to have
integrity, Teach.
[SHIRO] I'm afraid this
string of disgraces
is taking a toll on your
once loyal constituents.
This is where Itona comes in.
Um, okay. He's mumbling to
himself and it's getting weird.
Strong, stronger. Strongest!
[BOTH gasp]
Wait, he's got tentacles, too?
[SHIRO] The Silver Berserker is
obsessed with strength, you see.
On his head are
grafted appendages
similar to your teacher's.
An extreme decision, to be sure,
but dedication is what
separates a Demon King
from washed-up has-beens.
I am the Demon King!
[yells]
[gasps]
Look out, sir!
Whoa, look at him! He's actually
matching Koro-sensei's speed!
[SHIRO]
That's the way, Itona.
Kill him good. I'm ghost.
[KORO-SENSEI]
Yana-- I-I mean, Shiro!
Don't look at him, look at me!
Oh, no, this is bad.
Yeah, but for who?
You don't think
Koro-sensei's met his match?
[FUWA]
It's not that.
This series is a comedy!
The show's tone just took a 180!
What does that even mean?
The concept was supposed
to be light-hearted!
[NAGISA]
Koro-Q!
[GOOD BOYS &amp; GIRLS]
"Students on Duty"!
[KAEDE] There you go!
Grow nice and big now.
[TOKA]
Oh!
Hey, maybe we ought'a
water your chest?
[KAEDE chuckles nervously]
[KAEDE]
What are you implying?
Koro-Q!
You don't have what it
takes to be the Demon King.
The title belongs to me!
[KORO-SENSEI]
You really have your heart
set on taking my
place, don't you?
Don't be so
single-minded, my boy.
A hero casts his net wide,
becomes a jack-of-all-trades.
Same holds true for Demon Kings.
Fat lot of good the
title does anyone
if all we get is
bragging rights.
What are you talking about?
[KORO-SENSEI]
What indeed.
Making its glorious debut.
An E-class original production!
[BOTH] Ta-da! "Who's
Your Big Bad, One!"
When the heck did
you make that?!
True Big Bads, conversely
known as Demon Kings,
are as smart as they are strong.
And since we have a
challenger to the throne,
let's test the current ruler and
the newbie on their abilities!
Are you ready for
stage one? Right.
True villains kidnap people.
As a Big Bad, what would you do
if you kidnapped a princess?
Uh! Why am I the
princess in this?
[KARMA, NAKAMURA chuckling]
[KARMA] Don't mind us, folks.
On with the show.
[NAGISA]
I get enough of this at home!
Contestants, your answers?
[TOKA]
Yes! Koro-sensei?
[KORO-SENSEI] I'd offer
her a full-body massage,
a makeover, complete with
manicure, pedicure, an eyebrow--
[buzzer]
[ding]
[TOKA]
Yes! Itona?
Well, I would...
...challenge her to a battle
and prove I'm stronger!
I don't wanna fight!
[KARMA]
Heh. What a joke.
The two of you are
completely hopeless.
Ooo, the Red Devil has
entered the battle!
Your answer, contestant three!
[KARMA] First off, I would
tease him mercilessly
about how he looks the dress.
You put me in this thing!
[dinging]
End round one.
Karma gets ten points.
[KIMURA]
Justice!
[GOOD BOYS &amp; GIRLS]
"Students on Duty"!
[MEG]
Almost harvest time.
[ISOGAI] They said we can
keep whatever we pick.
My family might get a
decent meal this spring.
[MEG] What sort of flowers
should we put in afterwards?
[ISOGAI] I'm thinkin' potatoes,
a few carrots, some bok choy.
Ooo! And maybe green beans.
And onions. I love onions.
Oh! There might even be
room for mustard greens!
[MEG]
Well, at least it's practical.
Koro-Q!
It's time for round two!
In scientific terms, the Demon
King is an apex predator.
We all know that those at the
top have to maintain their cool.
So whatever happens next,
be sure to keep a straight face!
[IRINA giggles]
[IRINA] Are you bewitched
by my bodacious bod?
[TOKA] Who said I was
willing to do this?
[chuckles]
[KORO-SENSEI]
I told you.
Status-effect magic
has no power over me.
[buzzer]
Nice try, pervert!
I dunno how he's doing it,
but Itona's unfazed!
Dude, are you made of stone?
I take it back, he's a pig!
[buzzer]
[OKAJIMA]
Here.
You'll need these.
You need aversion therapy!
No points. Aw. So sad.
[NAKAMURA]
Koro-Q!
[GOOD BOYS &amp; GIRLS]
"Students On Duty"!
[FUWA] So the whole
point of these cutaways
is to make fun of us.
Kinds sucks bein'
the butt of a joke.
[KIRARA]
Life is a joke.
[FUWA]
Koro-Q!
[NAGISA]
The bitter fight to crown
the next Demon King rages on.
Tell us the one thing a true
Demon King has to be wary of!
Helicopter parents, of course!
[buzzer]
It doesn't get much more
brutal than a Demon King.
Give us all your most
brutal taunt go!
You weakling! You will
be forever a zero!
[KAEDE]
Say what?!
[buzzer]
Right! We're down to
the game's final round!
The last and most
difficult challenge
will be a scary
no-tears face off!
And here's where we find out
which of our determined
contestant has the ugliest,
most spine-chillingly
terrifying expression!
[KORO-SENSEI] I have a
proposition for you, Itona.
Once the match is done,
why not join E-class?
You're kidding, right?
I didn't come here
to join your class.
I came here to take your place.
[KORO-SENSEI]
You're a gifted young man,
but I'm richer in experience.
I use that experience to teach.
The way to beat me isn't to
hone in on my weaknesses,
but to absorb my lessons!
Are you saying... that I'm weak?
Alrighty, let's get
to it! Contestants.
[BOTH]
Go!
[chuckles]
I am the new Demon King!
Life's only guarantee is death.
[BOTH scream]
[KIRARA chuckles]
[KIRARA] What? You expect me to
sit on the sidelines for this?
Um, the winner is, uh, Hazama?
[KORO-SENSEI]
Do what?!
Technically she wasn't
up for the title,
but her evil game is strong.
She's the party member
you wouldn't wanna
meet in a dark alley.
Honestly I almost
feel bad for you,
but the only way to
beat this demon...
Heh.
...is by absorbing my darkness!
[KORO-SENSEI]
Cut that out!
Aw, c'mon, what's the matter,
Teach? Are ya scared?
[CLASS laughing]
[ITONA]
Wait.
Does a Demon King need to
have a sense of humor?
[BOTH]
What?!
[SHIRO]
Screw this!
[KORO-SENSEI] Whoa, whoa, whoa!
Wait, what are you doing?
You can't just yank them off
like that! Itona, stop!
Don't be so impulsive!
Come back!
What about joining our party?
Don't walk away!
Well, whaddya say we tidy up?
[CLASS]
Yes, Demon Queen!
[bell tolls]
[SUGINO]
Hey, Koro-sensei,
what ever happened
to that Itona guy?
[KORO-SENSEI] I invited him
to join us, but to no avail.
Ugh. Man, that really sucks.
Having all three legendary
warriors would've been sweet.
[CLASS yelps]
[KORO-SENSEI]
Uh? Ah! You came back!
Yeah, Shiro basically
told me to get lost.
He was all mad because I pulled
out my stupid tentacles.
Anyway, I'm kinda
out of options.
By the way, that's gonna
be my schitck now.
[CLASS]
He really is worse.