Yep. I get the feeling we've
come to the right place.
Pretty obvious spot for
a legendary item, huh?
Come on. Why's this on us?
Can't someone else grab
the stupid thing?
Oh, don't be that way.
We want in good with the Pope.
He's needs a replacement for
the one the Big Five broke.
Well, yeah, and we need it
to defeat the Demon King.
So there's that.
Quit being such an octo-wuss!
[KORO-SENSEI] I'm telling
you it's a Pandora's Box!
We open it at our peril!
Some hideous, boss-level monster
lies coiled within...
How's the Demon King
more scared than we are?
Wow, Professor
Bitch came along.
Of course I did! Ha-ha!
Rumor has it the world's
Skimpiest Magical Bikini
is hidden in this chest.
And I want it!
Not even Karasuma can
resist such power!
Yes, I can.
[OKAJIMA]
Uhh, details please.
[IRINA]
Huh?
Tell us more about
this "magical bikini."
Would her ladyship
prefer some help
in trying on said garment?
[MEG]
She most certainly would not!
[KAEDE] Since when is
a cave a dressing room?
Um, thanks, Mosquito
Bite Squad, but chill.
Can it, pimple-prick!
[MEG]
Hey, Nagisa.
Why don't we go ahead
and open the, uh--
[NAGISA]
Yeah. Sure thing.
Um, here goes.
What? Nobody wants
to say "chest" now?
What the--?
Okay, uh. It's empty.
[NAGISA]
Hmm.
Way to manage our expectations.
[BOTH gasp]
[OKAJIMA]
No!
This isn't happening,
this isn't happening,
this isn't happening!
Did we--?
Oh my God.
[ITONA screams]
Itona, what--?
[KORO-SENSEI]
Over here.
[ITONA]
What twisted magic is this?
What is this? Why have
I turned into Kaede?
I have way bigger boobs
than I'm used to.
Huh. That's what's going on.
Our bodies have pulled
the ol' switcheroo on us.
I'm totally Isogai. What a trip.
And I'm Maehara.
Seems like a serious violation
of privacy if you ask me.
And why do I feel a draft?
Oh, come on!
Our clothes shouldn't
be part of the bargain!
Um, sir? How's that a thing?
[ITONA] Well, I suppose
given our predicament,
logic dictates a bug resides
more in one's mind
than in the flesh,
meaning when we transfer
to a new physical form,
our quirks follow.
[KORO-SENSEI]
Hey, knock it off!
I look weird when you do that!
[ITONA]
Sorry.
The point is, Isogai's
equipment shortage
is a function of
his programming.
Even when manifested
in Maehara's body,
it remains in the old one.
[ISOGAI]
So I'm screwed?
[MEG yells]
Let me down!
Kataoka?
This isn't fair!
Come on! Just let me
have this, damn it!
Please don't look, Isogai!
Um, over here.
I can't keep up!
So Kataoka's Okajima now?
I feel sorry for Meg.
I lucked out getting
to be Kaede.
Could be worse, right?
This is what it feels like
to go from being a
have-not to a have-lots!
Just so you know, I am never
giving these back ever!
Excuse me?!
Hey, did anybody see what
happened to Professor Bitch?
Now that you mention it,
where's Commander K?
[KARASUMA]
No! Stop it!
I won't submit to
your evil wiles!
[KARASUMA snickers]
[IRINA]
If you rip out a button,
I swear by all that is sacred--
Put my cape back on!
[KARASUMA] Oh, my.
My rags come off so easily!
Hey, quit making
my face do that!
Not you, too, Isogai!
I thought you were
better than this!
The girl knows
how to multitask.
This is terrible.
[RYUNOSUKE]
There's something up ahead.
[BOTH]
Huh?
We keep pushing forward,
we might find a way
to undo all this.
Wait a sec. Why didn't
the two of you swap?
[BOTH] What? Can you
not tell the difference?
I'm Chiba. That's Hayami.
[ALL] You two were
meant for each other!
[HAYAMI]
Koro-Q.
Don't get me wrong, I'm happy
to stand guard and all,
but d'you think Rinka
and the others are okay?
I dunno.
I'd be surprised if Karma
can do much with my body.
Well, they got Koro-sensei
and Commander K with 'em,
so they ought'a be
in good shape.
[KUNUDONS laughing]
Abandon all hope,
ye who venture this far!
[chuckles]
I may be inhabiting
an unfamiliar form,
but my speed is
more than intact.
[ITONA chuckling]
[yelps]
[screaming]
[KORO SENSEI]
What did you do?
Seems I neglected to factor in
the relative rigidity
of human limbs.
[KORO SENSEI] Classic slapstick.
Let me learn from you!
I need you to focus!
'Kay, I'll tell ya what.
You handle this and
we'll keep going.
[IRINA]
This is your fight, too!
Must be rough
without his comic foil.
Good thing we're not
that kind of double act.
Look, if we don't
reverse this spell,
Okajima's gonna
have a field day.
[NAGISA]
That was a whole lot a' nothin'.
Huh?
Oh, crap.
[KARASUMA] All right, just
think about it for a second.
If some big scary
dungeon boss shows up
and starts wailing on us,
we'll be sittin' ducks!
Don't worry, we'll protect you.
Maehara and I
have similar builds,
so adjusting hasn't been
as difficult as it could be.
Believe me, holding our own
won't be awkward in the least.
[OKAJIMA, TOKA]
He's so manly even with
his butt hangin'
outta somebody else.
[KAEDE]
Hmm...
Okajima seems quiet,
don't you think?
He's alive, right?
What if the rope is cutting
off his circulation?
[MAEHARA] Maybe we should give
it some slack, just in case.
[OKAJIMA]
Probably a good idea.
I mean, he hasn't tried anything
and he looks so pitiful.
Now this is what
I call role-play.
Oh-ho, yeah. Papa may've
found himself a new hobby.
[screams]
[OKAJIMA]
Definitely NSFW! Look away!
[ISOGAI]
Actually, those are my eyes!
Um, what was that?
Hey. What's wrong?
I just feel sorta
weird all of a sudden.
Like maybe something's
happened to my real body.
Call it a sense of foreboding.
What do you mean?
You think Karma might be
in some kind of trouble?
Could be. I should go
look. You stay here.
Wait! Nagisa!
We're coming, too!
What happened?
[MAEHARA]
Guys! There's a hidden room!
[KARMA]
Chiba! Hayami!
[IRINA]
Huh?
[HAYAMI]
Hey.
Where's Karma?
[TOKA gasps]
[TOKA]
Look!
Oh, no! It can't be!
[KARMA]
Karma!
Avert your eyes, Nagisa!
Is it that bad?
[KARMA]
Seriously?
The world's skimpiest bikini
fits you like a glove!
What possessed you
to try it on?!
I tried to make him
stop. I really did.
'S girls-only armor, but
you're still able to wear it.
No surprise!
[KORO SENSEI]
It does look good on you.
Not really the point!
Hey, we found another chest!
Ah! I do believe
that's a Swap Orb!
Right, boys 'n girls,
if we use this,
we should revert back
to our old selves.
Well, what are we waiting
for? Let's do it!
[ALL scream]
Huh? Where'm I now?
Did that thing work?
[BOTH]
We're us.
[MEG]
Yes!
I'm back! Ha-ha! Thank you!
I feel like myself again!
Ugh. I almost tasted bliss.
[KAEDE] Back to being
one of the have-nots.
Aw, sweetie. Don't be sad.
Glad that's over. Let's get
outta this place, guys.
Sounds like a plan.
You ready to go, sir?
Koro-sensei? Hello?
Wait a sec.
He's not still Itona?
[ITONA]
No, I'm me.
[MEG]
Hm?
So what's the problem?
Cat got your tongue?
Hey, Koro-sensei?
[screams]
[KORO-SENSEI] Why am I wearing
the Demon King's skin?
I surrender! This magic is
way beyond my pay-grade!
[CLASS]
What was that about?
[RYUNOSUKE]
Uh. Uh-oh...
[gasping]
[KUNUDON A]
Ah! Wait! Come back!
That's my body you're
running away with!
Uh... excuse me. I'm still here.