[IRINA humming]
So you're, uh, sure you know
what you're doing, miss?
Cut me some slack, sweetheart.
It's in the name, Irina
Jelavich, the Seductive Witch.
You wanna kick, you came
to the right enchantress.
Those silly little boys will
be knocked on their asses!
You promise?
Commander K, look out!
Hey, we're fine with making
chocolates ourselves.
It's really no big deal.
[IRINA]
Shush.
Just sit back, hun,
and watch a master of the
dark arts strut her stuff.
Um, that "stuff" looks rank.
[IRINA cackling]
[MAEHARA]
No kidding?
You're giving this to me?
Jerk. Got a problem?
I'll take 'em back!
[MAEHARA]
No, no! I'm totally stoked!
Oh, sweet!
Yeah, don't get too excited.
Just consider it an apology
for all the crap I give you.
[TOKA] Here ya go, fellas.
Happy Valentines Day.
I know it's just because
you're nice, but wow, thanks!
Where's Karasuma? Aw, c'mon.
I really wanted to give
him these chocolates.
Why's he gotta be gone today?
[SUGINO]
Woo!
[screams]
[SUGINO]
Yes! Yes! Yes!
[KANZAKI chuckles]
[KANZAKI]
I'm, uh, glad you like them.
Jeez, get a grip, dude.
I know it's a dream
come true, but still.
Gah, these are so good!
I'm gonna wolf down
the whole box!
[KIMURA]
I know, right? Me, too!
Are there anymore?
Please tell me you've got more.
[gasps]
[BOTH] Chocolate. Chocolate.
Chocolate. Chocolate.
[TOKA screams]
Was this supposed to happen?
[OKUDA]
Hm?
That's not good.
The love potion
Professor Bitch made
contains a highly
addictive compound!
Do what now?!
Yes.
These chocolates have the effect
of making people...
crave... chocolate!
Holy crap!
[HINANO screams]
[HINANO]
Uh! Get away from me!
[TOKA]
Is it just me,
or did Professor Bitch
not prepare us for this?
Whoa, whoa! Back off!
These are for me!
[OKAJIMA]
Chocolate!
Don't even try, pervert!
And drop the act already
since nobody gave you
anything to begin with!
Go away! Hyah!
This from Kanzaki!
Lay a hand on it and you die!
You're seriously protective
of your chocolate.
Damn right! I was gonna keep
it as a family heirloom.
But desperate times!
Sugino! Don't tell me Kanzaki
was in on this, too!
Nuh-uh.
I totally grabbed it from the
bargain aisle yesterday.
[KANZAKI screams]
I'm invincible!
[NAGISA, MAEHARA]
Uh, what the hell?!
What's worse? Zombies
or Sugino is beast mode?
Yeah, that would be his bug.
Whenever Sugino reaches
peak excitement levels,
he goes full-on berserker.
Huh. That's good to know.
--[crash]
--[SUGINO roars]
What do we do? We have
to rein the poor guy in!
Little easier said than
done at the moment.
[ALL]
Chocolate. Chocolate! Chocolate!
I've got it! Listen up!
You can have all the chocolate
you want if you stop Sugino!
[ALL yelling]
[NAKAMURA sighs]
'Least we bought ourselves
a little time, yeah?
It sounds like a battle
royale out there.
Is there zombie juice
in the ones you gave me?
Huh?! What is wrong with you?!
Newsflash, jerkwad,
it's rude to ask a girl
if she poisoned your
Valentine's present!
[SUGINO howling]
[MAEHARA sighs]
Man, yesterday was
a total cluster.
Sorry for getting swept up
in the zombie rampage.
But thank goodness the
effects only last 24 hours.
If only that were
true for Sugino.
[ISOGAI] What do you mean
you're transferring?!
C'mon, Takebayashi,
you can't just leave!
Oh, I assure you, I can.
[KOYAMA snickering]
[NAGISA]
What are you guys talking about?
[KAEDE]
And what's he doing here?
[NAKAMURA]
Takebayashi is dropping E-class
to join the paladins.
Or as I like to put it,
spreading my wings and leaving
you losers in the dust.
Way too good a deal to pass up.
[KARMA]
Spreading your wings, huh?
More like flappin'
your dorsal fin.
Explain to me why an elite
group of mage-warriors
would cherry pick a
nobody from this dump?
Definitely something
suspicious here.
Maybe they want Koro-sensei--
Oh, right, my bad,
I meant to say Demon King.
[KAEDE gasps]
Someone should
review their priorities!
We're supposed to be
in this together!
[TAKEBAYASHI] Like when everyone
got all bent outta shape
over a little chocolate?
If I had any doubts before
yesterday, they're gone now.
This class is the
bottom of the barrel.
You can't really mean that.
I have no choice
here but to secede.
Staying isn't going to win
the approval of my parents.
I want a future--
a chance to shine.
And most importantly...
...Valentine's Day Chocolate.
From upwardly mobile paladin!
That's your main motivation?!
You really need to calm down.
We're gonna need a better
reason than that.
[TAKEBAYASHI]
You guys are popular.
You wouldn't understand.
[ISOGAI, MAEHARA]
Uh?
Of all the postcards
on Shinjuku Promenade,
mine were the very
last ones to be taken!
What are you doing?!
Don't share that kind of thing!
No one would've known
if you hadn't said it!
Would've known what?!
[TAKEBAYASHI]
Koro-Q.
Let me go, damn it!
I'm joining the paladins
and getting chocolate for...
Okay. Now what?
That should hold him
for a little while.
I-I can't believe after
everything we've been through...
'S gotta be something'll
make him wanna stay.
We can't defeat Koro-sensei
unless we do it as a group.
I have the perfect idea.
Lemme go!
[GIRLS]
Hello, master!
If it's maids you want,
there are plenty... right here!
[OKAJIMA]
We've died and gone to heaven!
[SUGINO]
Kanzaki!
Ugh. I feel so gross.
Why does anyone dress like this?
Don't look. It's creepy.
Uh. Yeah. What she said.
I'm hating how well
you pull this off.
[KARMA snickers]
[TOKA] So anything master
wants in particular?
Just say the word and
your wish is our command.
What have you done with Yada?!
This is straight up ero-tech
from Professor Bitch herself.
Guaranteed to keep
any man where he is.
[OKAJIMA, MAEHARA, TOKA]
So why isn't it working?!
[TAKEBAYASHI] Being my maid
is no simple matter!
To wit, first she must
relinquish one whole dimension!
There were boobs in his face
and he didn't even flinch?!
What evil magic is this?!
[TOKA]
Koro-Q!
Perk up. No point
bein' so negative.
E-class has its
share of good points.
[TAKEBAYASHI]
Huh.
That's hilarious.
You idiots have even less
screen time than I do.
[KIMURA, SUGAYA scream]
And yet you... still
got your chocolate!
That's your biggest issue?
As a class, we are more
than the sum of our parts.
[TAKEBAYASHI] You're still
the imposter, aren't you?
[MAEHARA] There's just no
getting through to him.
[ISOGAI] Anyone figured
out why the teachers
haven't bothered to show up yet?
[MEG]
This is hopeless.
[RITSU]
No, it's not!
Give me a chance
to turn this around.
[NAKAMURA]
Ritsu?
Ever since joining E-class,
I've made it a point
of closely monitoring
our development.
If there's one thing
I'm certain of,
it's that we can only
succeed as a team.
Friends with the same goal.
Please standby while
I calculate the best way
of getting Takebayashi
back on board.
Ah. Yes. I'll simply
use my magic.
Okay.
I'm picking up
some serious power!
[RITSU]
Takebayashi?
Stay with us, please.
We need you.
[gasps]
[CLASS]
Takebayashi!
Um, what just happened?
[RITSU]
Sorcery.
No, but really.
[RITSU]
Sorcery.
Hey! What are you eating?!
Just don't sweat the
small stuff, you know?
It's hard to be uptight when
you've seen what I have.
Name of the game
is chill, trust me.
Life is too short.
[TAKABAYASHI sighs]
Anyway, if you still want
me to be part of the team,
I s'pose I'm game.
[ISOGAI]
I, uh, don't quite understand
what changed your mind,
but you're sticking
around, so...
[MEG] What kind of magic
did you use exactly?
[RITSU]
It's a secret.
♪ As the seasons come... ♪
[NAGISA]
He's singing?
♪ My true love disappears
behind a cloud. ♪
♪ Like the sun 'cause that's
the way of new beginnings. ♪
♪ Let's take it slow. ♪
♪ Until the day I see
you in a crowd. ♪
♪ And mem'ry sings what
could have been. ♪
♪ Until the day when our
hearts will meet again. ♪