[bell tolls]
[NAGISA] Starting today, Royal
Knight Commander Karasuma
will be teaching E-class
the way of the sword.
This is a civilized weapon.
Mastery is it's own reward.
[CLASS gasps]
[SUGINO]
Holy crap!
[MAEHARA] He sliced off
that mountain's top knot!
Right, now it's your turn.
[MAEHARA, SUGINO]
Are you out of your mind?
[KORO-SENSEI]
Tadaomi Karasuma.
Arguably the most
feared and respected
swordsman in any world.
And he's actually
sharing the secrets
of his awesomeness with us!
This is sweet!
Oh, wow! The fact he's
so scary makes him hot!
This'll be a great way to get
to know him a little better!
[KORO-SENSEI]
Ee! Damn you, Karasuma!
You're trying to take my place
as their favorite teacher!
Attention, boys n' girls!
If you think his
technique is all that,
check out these
funky fresh moves!
Hyah! Now everyone hold your
weapons exactly as I am!
[CLASS]
Seriously?!
[KORO-SENSEI]
Heh-heh.
Observe what this stance
enables me to unleash!
That's not something
people can do!
What are the swords for
in this scenario?
[NAKAMURA]
Wow. Desperate much?
[OKAJIMA]
He's trying too hard.
[SUGINO] If I'm gonna
learn swordsmanship,
I want a human to teach me.
[KORO-SENSEI]
Blast! I'm losing them!
[NAGISA] On Commander's
Karasuma's recommendation,
the Crown approved
funds for E-class
to equip itself with weapons.
So here we are in the nearby
village to do some shopping.
Guy must have some
pull with the Big Wigs
if he can get 'em to green-light
something like this, am I right?
Yeah!
[KORO-SENSEI growls]
[KORO-SENSEI] That jerk is
siphoning off my popularity
with the young 'uns!
[NAGISA chuckles]
Sorry, 'fraid all I got in
stock are Irina Dumplings.
[CLASS]
Huh?
[MAEHARA]
Isn't this a weapons shop?
[NAKAMURA] What're we supposed
to do with dumplings?
[CLERK A] Trust me,
you'll never have juicier.
[CLASS]
What the--?
I'll take two!
[OKANO]
Guys!
The armory's only
selling Irina Crackers!
And all they have at the
item shop are Irina Cakes!
[MAEHARA]
You're kidding me!
Irina, how I adore
thee, mistress.
You are a golden goddess.
I worship you!
Is it just me or does something
seem off about this place?
Maybe.
[KORO-SENSEI]
"The Irina Soft-Serve
is a sugary revelation."
What is this, an eating tour?
[KORO-SENSEI]
Due diligence, Okajima!
If we're to uncover
what's going on,
no stone must be left unturned!
[CLASS]
Huh?
[KORO-SENSEI]
If you would, Mr. Village Chief.
Yes.
[VILLAGE CHIEF]
Things are not as they seem!
Our community is in
thrall to dark magic!
Brave travelers, I beg you!
Drive her out! Banish
the dread witch, Irina!
[CLASS]
Do what now?
[laughs]
[KORO-SENSEI]
Methinks this has potential
as an extracurricular lesson!
[NAGISA]
Koro-Q!
[KAEDE]
Tower of Temptation?
Kind of a skeezy name, isn't it?
[KORO-SENSEI]
Excuse us, anyone home?
[IRINA] Ah. Intrepid
wanderers. Fates be praised.
Water. Please?
I'm on the very verge
of death from thirst.
[KAEDE]
Sketchy!
[NAGISA] Pretty sure we should
stay away from her instead.
Here, milady, have ours.
What did Nagisa just say?!
I can't thank you enough.
[CLASS gasps]
[MAEHARA]
Done.
[chuckling]
[NAGISA] See? That's
what I'm talking about!
[chuckles]
Candy from a baby.
Now what's all this I hear
about you driving me out?
[KAEDE]
She really is a witch!
Yeah, sure, but wow!
I'm super jealous
of her cup size.
Hey, so, uh, what about me?
Oh, honey. You're not my type.
Ah! Don't be mean!
No, wait. That might
actually be my thing.
Yep. Totally is.
[CLASS]
Big shock.
[KORO-SENSEI]
I take it we're in the presence
of Irina Jelavich,
the Seductive Witch?
And if you are?
[KORO-SENSEI] Might I ask that
you kindly release the villagers
from your salacious enchantment?
Sorry, no can do.
I've grown accustomed to
a certain standard of living.
But let's change the subject.
You seem like a hardy bunch.
You'd make a fine addition
to the minion class.
Dream on, witch!
You're not gonna seduce us!
[HINANO, OKANO] Yeah, we're
impervious to your magic!
[GUYS gasping]
[NAKAMURA, HINANO, OKANO]
Guys.
[IRINA sighing]
[chuckling]
[NAGISA] Fight, Koro-sensei!
Keep it together!
[KORO-SENSEI]
Insta-killed by cleavage!
Really?! Come on!
Way to go, perv!
No fair!
Why do big boobs have
so much power over men?
Welcome to the team, boys.
Take care of these
dorks, will you?
I'll be upstairs, slipping into
something more comfortable.
Oh, and...
[GIRLS scream]
[NAGISA]
Oh, no! This is bad!
There we are.
You shorties are
gonna help Momma
develop a new charm
that works on women.
Doesn't that sound fun?
[SUGINO]
Ugh! Move it!
[GUYS]
Commander K?!
Hey! I can handle these idiots!
Go ahead and make sure
the witch is stopped!
[GUYS]
Yes, sir!
[ISOGAI]
Koro-Q!
Fish in a barrel.
The menfolk are
always such chumps.
[KAEDE]
Then why be so proud about
wrapping them around
your little finger?
You're not fooling us.
No way that full-figured bod's
not just some kind of illusion.
[HINANO]
Wait, her boobs are fake?
Shut up!
Ugh! I ought'a magic
those big mouths shut!
Release them at once!
Nagisa!
Huh? What the hell?
How'd you nobodies get up here?
Doesn't matter.
The more slavishly devoted
minions, the merrier!
Shazam!
[GUYS gasp]
Great. So now what're
we supposed to do?
[KARMA]
Hm.
She's been playing that charm
close to the chest, heh.
But if we got it away from her,
the spell'd be broken.
[gasps]
Yeah? So what if it
would, carrot top?
[KARMA]
Nailed it.
Like you've got the grapes
to yank this baby outta my hand!
Get 'em, boys! I'm tired
of lookin' at their faces!
I was going to let
you leave here alive,
but since you know
my weak point...
Too bad they had
to be so damn pure.
Oh, well, c'est la vie.
[GIRLS]
Nagisa! Karma!
[IRINA] This is what happens
when snot-nosed pubescent punks
stick their noses
in grownup business.
Buh-bye now.
[BOTH scream]
[BOTH gasp]
[gasps]
[KORO-SENSEI] Whew! That was
almost too close for comfort.
Son of a--! You're supposed
to be under my spell!
[KORO-SENSEI]
Madam, please.
Your magic has no power over me.
What do you take me
for, a trash mob?
Do your homework.
Status-effect enchantments have
no power over the Demon King!
Go figure.
Heh. Knew it all along!
Nice fake-out there, Teach.
[KORO-SENSEI chuckles]
[KORO-SENSEI]
Toying with you has been a lark,
but trying to push my students
out a window to their deaths
is a bridge too far.
Nice try, Jaw Breaker!
I'm not sure what's going on,
but don't pat yourself
on the back just yet.
I still have hostag-- Huh?
Not anymore you don't.
I've taken the liberty
of setting them free.
[IRINA]
What?!
[KARASUMA] This thing told me
his plan on the first floor.
[KORO-SENSEI]
Easy, easy! I'm only pretending!
Gah! He broke the
cage in one blow!
Coolest thing I've seen
in my entire life!
Same. I think I'm
falling in love.
[KORO-SENSEI] Gah!
No, no, no! This was my idea!
Why are they all
smitten with you?
I don't know!
[KORO-SENSEI] And what about
your immunity to Irina's charms?
I'm the Demon King,
so of course she couldn't
get a foothold on me,
but are you sure you don't
bat for the other team?
[KARASUMA]
It's called being disciplined!
Game, set, match.
Admit defeat, foul witch.
[KORO-SENSEI] Someone's
been a naughty sorceress.
Whatever are we to do?
[screams]
[IRINA]
Ah! No, please! Stop!
I-I'll be a good girl
from now on, I swear.
Cross my heart.
I beg your forgiveness.
[GUYS]
What did they do to her?
[grunting]
[ALL]
What is wrong with you?!