[screams]
[HERO] I am the Prince of
the Fateful Eternal Wind.
My journey is endless.
[IRON KUNUDON B]
Anyone have a clue
what this guy's babbling about?
[IRON KUNUDON C] I don't know,
but he sounds confident!
[VILLAGER A]
We are in your debt, good sir!
Such bravery will be
spoken of for ages!
Nay. You are too kind.
Now, then.
Methinks there are no
monsters left to slay
in these lonesome hills.
Where shall I venture next?
[NAGISA]
Our tale begins a year ago,
when Koro-sensei,
the Demon King,
also known as the Big Bad,
was still human.
[YANAGISAWA]
Look sharp: We've got customers.
No sleeping on the
clock, troglodytes.
Morning, welcome to
the Temple of Trades.
Dissatisfied with your job?
Let us relocate you to one
more suited to your skillset!
So what brings you
in to see us today?
I, uh, believe I've
gone as far as I can
in my current line of work.
Oh. And what line of
work might that be, sir?
There are many who would
refer to me as a hero.
Oh my goodness, I bet the hours
are absolutely dreadful.
Well now, I do endeavor
to give the quest my all.
'Tis the duty of
one so intrepid.
Sure, sure. 'Cept you're
not making much progress?
A shame after coming
as far as you have.
That must be
super-duper frustrating.
But I think I have
just the thing!
Really?
You're gonna love it!
A vacancy just opened
up the other day.
Yes, go on.
[AGURI] How do you feel
about being the Demon King?
[HERO]
You said this lair's called
the Castle of Darkness, correct?
I must confess, the ambiance
in here is wonderfully gloomy!
And I appreciate
your generous offer
to waive the security deposit.
You really didn't have
to do that, you know.
He'd hit a wall professionally
and decided it was
high time to move on.
I can relate.
I suppose any job gets
tiresome after a while.
Oh. And there he is now.
Welcome. I am the gentleman
you'll be replacing.
[HERO] I can't thank you enough
for coming all this way.
[NEURO]
My pleasure.
In a position like this,
the handoff is vital.
So... from Hero to Demon King
seems a rather long way to fall.
Forgive my asking,
but is the world really
so dreadful as all that?
My public will be
surprised, won't they?
[chuckles]
You will do beautifully.
This gig is no walk in the park,
but you seem ferocious enough.
You're too kind, sir. I hope
that I can do it justice.
What's next for you?
What indeed...
Alas, this place holds no
mystery for me anymore.
Charming though it once was.
I could journey to a new world,
or perhaps try my hand
at being a warlock.
Sounds exhilarating.
You'll have to regale me
with stories one day.
Yes, well, very best of
luck to you, my friend.
[HERO]
And to you.
[AGURI]
The Demon King's wardrobe!
You'll look fantastic
in this stuff!
Gracious, how thoughtful
of him to have left it.
[gasps]
[AGURI]
Uh-oh. Is something wrong?
[HERO screams]
[KORO-SENSEI] Uh! I think
the position is cursed!
You... look...
[KORO-SENSEI]
Gah! Avert your eyes!
I cannot bear to
be seen like this!
[AGURI]
...splendid!
[KORO-SENSEI]
Huh?
[NEURO]
Koro-Q.
[YAKO]
Hey!
Ha! I seek the Demon King!
[KORO-SENSEI]
Mew?
[NEWBIE HERO] So it's true!
You've turned to evil!
[KORO-SENSEI]
Huh?
Excuse me, young man, but, um,
do we know each other
from somewhere?
I'm your pupil! Don't tell
me you've forgotten!
Whatever all this is,
I demand an explanation!
[KORO-SENSEI]
What can I say?
Being a hero simply
lost its luster for me.
Of course, it turns out 80%
of what a Demon King does
is sit and brood.
You couldn't have picked
a better time to show up.
Newsflash: I'm not here
to alleviate your boredom.
I'm here to vanquish you!
[KORO-SENSEI] Aw. That's not
a very nice thing to say.
Do you have any idea how many
new monsters started showing up
the minute you turned your
back on the hero game?
I can't remember the last
time I got good sleep!
I've been so busy slaying,
my level is through
the friggin' roof!
[KORO-SENSEI]
Ah! Congratulations, m'boy!
I knew you had it in you!
Are you patronizing me?
Take a deep breath.
You're going to give
yourself an aneurism.
[NEWBIE HERO] Why do you
encourage him to do this?
You can change jobs, too.
Why stick with something that
makes you so miserable, right?
'Sides, no offense,
but you just don't seem
like the hero type.
Not what I needed
to hear, thanks.
But, yeah.
I suppose you're right.
It's the same thing
every day, y'know?
I'm sorry.
I mean, c'mon, is that
what it is to be a hero?
'Cause it feels like torture.
[AGURI] It doesn't sound like
there's much room for growth.
[KORO-SENSEI]
Bingo.
So what else is
out there for me?
Let's have a look, shall we?
Ooo! This one sounds fun!
[KORO-SENSEI, NEWBIE HERO]
What is it?
The Reaper! Perfect!
[AGURI]
Koro-Q!
[SHIRO]
Thank you, ladies and gentlemen.
We're thrilled to be here!
[SHIRO]
My name is Shiro.
I'm Yanagisawa.
[BOTH] And together:
We're One and the Same!
Thank you, you're
a marvelous crowd.
[SHIRO]
Anyone who can tell us apart
receives complimentary
passes to our next show.
That reminds me, Shiro.
[SHIRO]
Yes, Yanagisawa?
That "Shield of Earth" Barrier
really did a number
on you the other day.
[SHIRO]
Oh, that.
Just the government
playing with its toys.
More like molecular
gastronomy. Hey!
[SHIRO]
Comedy gold.
Parum-pum-pum.
You've been great.
[SHIRO, YANIGASAWA]
Koro-Q.
[AGURI]
Hello? Mr. Demon King?
How are things going?
Thought I'd stop by
for a follow-up. Huh?
Is this a bad time?
[KORO-SENSEI]
Power corrupts.
Absolute power
corrupts absolutely.
[AGURI]
You're bored again?
[KORO-SENSEI]
Yes. Ugh.
The novelty sustained me
for a little while, but...
Not a single warrior has proven
equal to the task of facing me.
I tidied up the castle,
tended to monsters,
hid treasures in dungeons
all over the land,
day after day after day.
[AGURI]
All by yourself?
[KORO-SENSEI]
Did I mention trap maintenance?
Oh, there's been a lot of that.
[AGURI] Sounds like you've
really thrown yourself
into the work.
[KORO-SENSEI]
Yet no one dared to come
and throw down the gauntlet.
The seasons marched on.
And suddenly: Eureka!
[AGURI]
Yes?
[KORO-SENSEI] I thought,
why not train warriors
to take me on?
Oh! Greatest idea ever!
[KORO-SENSEI]
Right?
That's splendid!
[KORO-SENSEI] Couldn't have
said it better myself!
[KORO-SENSEI]
So there you have it.
That's what brings
me to E-class.
An ingenious solution,
if I do say so myself.
[KORO-SENSEI chuckles]
So then, what became
of your former pupil?
[KORO-SENSEI] Oh, he accepted
the Reaper position
and promptly disappeared
without a trace.
Kudos to reinventing yourself!
That doesn't sound very good.
[bell tolls]
[KORO-SENSEI]
Mew?
Time to mold young minds!
I believe today we'll
focus on magic potions
and how best to use them
against a foe of my stature.
Oh, I forgot the bring
the forbidden tome
I borrowed from Okajima!
Excuse me!
So regardless of his past,
he's, uh, he's the
Demon King now, right?
Because I'd swear it looks
like he's having fun.
Yeah, well, whatever the
hell you wanna call him,
he sure loves being a teacher.
[KORO-SENSEI] Moral of
the story, boys n' girls:
Enjoy the climb.
Reach the summit too
soon or too easily
and you'll want
to change careers.
[CLASS]
What're you talking about?
[KORO-SENSEI]
Embrace the chance to fail.
What better way to know the path
than falling onto it face-first
every now and then?
[CLASS]
What does that even mean?
[KORO-SENSEI] Okajima,
here's the book you loaned me.
Thanks again!
You have to do this now?!
Late again, huh?
Oh, well. Big shock.
Well, as long as the kids are
learning and he's having fun.
Lucky dog!
[NEURO]
Out with it!
Reveal to me the ultimate
mystery and satisfy my hunger!
[NEURO chuckles]
Y-Yusei Matsui's next
project is gonna be--
[FUWA]
You're in the wrong show!