[KORO-SENSEI]
Exciting news!
We have a fresh-faced transfer
student joining E-class today!
Is it a girl? Say yes!
Heh-heh.
Just so happens I have
a photograph of her
from Commander Karasuma.
[MAEHARA]
Whoa! She's perfect!
[OKAJIMA]
I know! She's so totally hot!
[MAEHARA]
Check out her boobs!
Could you be any
more disgusting?!
Down with ta-tas!
[NAGISA]
Okay then.
[CLASS]
Uh.
What's with the rock?
I am the Autonomous
Intelligence Magic Stone Tablet.
Pleased to meet you.
[CLASS]
Witchcraft!
So how come the new
girl's just a big rock?
Excuse me, this is the
legendary Sage Tablet
on which the thaumaturges of old
collected their spells for
vanquishing Demon Kings.
She is a veritable textbook
of advanced applied sorcery.
Oh, I guess when
you put it like that...
Can she make my boobs bigger?!
Or teach me to stop time
for no particular reason?
Not what she's for!
The ancient ones ensured
she'd only be used
by good people, unselfishly.
So they gave her the capacity
for independent thought.
[KAEDE, OKAJIMA]
Wait, we're not good?
The benefits are many.
This permits me to wield
magic at my discretion.
For the solitary
purpose of eliminating
he known as the Demon King.
[KARMA]
Good for you.
Best a luck getting rid of him
with some dinky magic spell.
Do not fear, friend.
[gasps]
[KARMA]
Ohh...
[RITSU] I am able to
cast two spells at once,
combining them to create
a completely new attack.
[CLASS whimpers]
[RITSU]
This is my particular bug.
[CLASS]
Things are now officially weird.
Why does she have hands?
Is there a person in there?
Sorcery.
Are you sure?
Because it looks like
you're actually eating.
Still sorcery.
The rice bowl an illusion, too?!
Sorcery.
My magic uses a
great deal of HP,
so I must replenish regularly.
That's the price of
extraordinary powers.
More please.
[yelps]
[KARASUMA] She might actually
help us defeat this thing.
As of right now, she's a member
of this class. Any objections?
[KORO-SENSEI]
None at all, my good man!
Welcome to the family,
Autonomous Intelligence
Magic Stone Tablet!
Zoom!
I wonder if I might ask
a teensy little favor.
Do you know any spells
for banishing pixilation?
[RITSU] I am forbidden from
instructing a Demon King
in the ways of magic.
But yes.
[BOTH]
I knew it!
An ingenious thamaturge spent
his whole life concocting one.
[OKAJIMA]
He must've been very wise.
[MAEHARA] Yeah, so wise.
All he did was look at porn!
[RITSU]
Koro-Q.
[KORO-SENSEI]
Okie-dokie, boys n' girls!
This will be your first quest
with our new party member!
I expect every one
of you to level up!
[CLASS]
Yes, sir!
So you need a better name.
[TOKA] "Autonomous Intelligence
Magic Stone Tablet"
is a lot to say.
[RITSU] I once vanquished
a band of savage plunderers
from the bowels of a
remote northern cave.
The battle earned
me the peculiar
but apt nickname:
Ritsu, the Evolved Mage.
[ALL] Why does that
story sound oddly familiar?
Oh, so that's who you are!
You're one of the warriors
Commander Karasuma
mentioned in episode two!
For continuity, I draw your
attention to the Red Devil.
Um, what?
Great, then we'll
call you Ritsu, too!
[TOKA]
She doesn't like that name?
[CLASS]
Holy crap, she can walk!
[MEG]
On itty-bitty feet!
Enemies at 12 o'clock!
Analysis done.
Stone Monsters. Attacks are
heavy, but quite subtle.
What's that mean?
[STONE KUNUDON A]
I got this hot chick's number
and hit her up with
"how you livin'?"
It's been four days.
She never texted me back.
[MEG]
Heavy, but subtle.
[NAGISA]
I feel kind of bad.
Allow me to handle them, please.
Combo spell:
Flame Rain!
[STONE KUNUDONS screaming]
Damn, she's good!
Yeah! That's the way, Ritsu!
Petrify.
[KAEDE]
What are you doing?
We're turning to stone!
[RITSU]
I defeated the enemy by myself.
Therefore, I alone am entitled
to experience points.
Since incapacitated party
members do not gain XP,
I have temporarily frozen you.
[MAEHARA]
Not cool!
Um, Ritsu? Little much back
there, don't'cha think?
[RITSU]
I have calculated the odds
of defeating the Demon King
and determined it more efficient
for me to level up exponentially
rather than all party
members doing so together.
[CLASS sighs]
We're s'posed to be a team.
[RITSU]
I advise we move on.
[MAEHARA]
Koro-Q!
Ritsu, help a guy out
with a healing spell?
I am afraid I can't
do that, Okajima.
The number of enemies you
can destroy at full health
compared to the amount of magic
I would have to use to heal you
renders that proposition
unsustainable.
Yeah, well you're unsustainable!
[NAGISA]
In the end,
Ritsu's hoarded all
the experience points,
and she kept every
item we picked up.
[CLASS groans]
[KORO-SENSEI sighs]
[KORO-SENSEI]
Young lady.
I can't stress enough
how important it is
that you get along with
your fellow classmates.
[RITSU]
Get along?
To what purpose?
I can vanquish
you all by myself!
[KORO-SENSEI yelping]
[RITSU]
My combo magic doesn't faze him.
Could he have adapted?
[KORO-SENSEI] Oh, my! What
dainty fingers you've got there!
[RITSU] Is he giving the
Evolved Mage a manicure?
[KORO-SENSEI] Let me show you
a little something, if I may.
You don't know pain!
Not till your wife leaves you!
And the boss tells
ya to get lost!
And you're stuck
with chronic illness!
The kind insurance won't touch!
[NAGISA]
This one's Level 19.
[CLASS]
That's even heavier.
[OLD MAN KUNUDON A]
I'm gonna teach you little brats
how hard life really is!
[KORO-SENSEI]
So how do you think they'll do?
How will they do?
Even as a group they're no
match for the likes of him.
Let me take care of this.
[KORO-SENSEI]
Children!
Time to unveil the you-know-what
you've been working on
in secret after school!
[NAGISA, KAEDE]
How did you know?!
No point tryin' to hide it
if the target's just
busted you, right?
Oh, fine. Let's do this, Nagisa!
[OKUDA] A blaze dwells
within this blade!
[KAEDE]
Flaming sword of fire!
[BOTH] Burn with offense-buffing
light. Mighty Aura!
Ready?
Yep!
[NAGISA, KARMA]
Fiery Cross Slash!
[KORO-SENSEI chuckles]
[CLASS]
We did it!
[STONE KUNUDON CHILD A]
Daddy, no!
[STONE KUNUDON CHILD B]
Papa!
[STONE KUNUDON
CHILDREN shouting]
[MAEHARA]
No one told me he had a family!
That's pretty heavy stuff.
It'll all be okay.
Are you ever gonna
change back?
[KORO-SENSEI] Wouldn't you agree
that the odds of defeating me
increase significantly
if you all work together?
Well, theoretically, yes.
[KORO-SENSEI chuckles]
[KORO-SENSEI] Then let's
put theory to the test
and beef up your cooperation
skills outside of class.
Be careful on the way back,
boys n' girls. See ya!
[CLASS gasps]
[BOTH]
Huh?
Ah, good morning, team!
How's it goin'?
[CLASS]
Wha--?!
Aw, guys! I'm just excited
we get to work together!
[NAGISA]
Who're you?
[KORO-SENSEI]
Ritsu, who else?
Well, mostly. Just improved.
I've been retooled to be
a better team player!
Excellent. Heh.
A two-D girl is
preferable anyway.
Takebayashi, seriously?
That's your first line?
How did you change
her overnight?
[KORO-SENSEI] You see, chiseled
on the tablet's flipside
in ancient script was
her operating spell.
Once I'd deciphered it,
tweaking our new
addition was elementary.
You can read and write
ancient languages?
I'm startin' to think there's
nothin' this guy can't do.
[KORO-SENSEI]
Moral of the story:
A good hero is a
jack of all trades.
So be sure not to neglect
your ancient language studies!
[CLASS]
Yes, sir!
[KORO-SENSEI]
ZIp!
Now, uh, getting back
to our little spell
for banishing pixilation
we talked about earlier.
That's not what she's for!