[DEMON LORD roars]
[SOLDIER A] We did it!
We beat the demon lord!
That means we won
the whole game!
Guess we're done
till the next update.
[BELPHE sighs] That boss
was brand new.
They finish this stuff as
fast as I throw it at them.
I'm gonna lose all my
subscribers at this rate.
I'd better cook up a new
expansion for these nerds.
[LEVI hums]
Next one on the list is
the Demon Lord of Sloth.
What can you tell me?
[LEVI hums]
She's strong,
but she's super lazy.
When she loses her temper,
she's real scary.
All she ever does
is lay around,
but she's somehow able to
get thousands of followers.
There anything else?
Uh... She runs some online
game thing with Mammon.
[LUCIFER]
"Online"?
[LEVI] Like, the internet?
That thing Maria uses?
Well, Sloth brought it to Hell.
[LUCIFER]
Hmm...
[LEVI hums]
Hey, look! It's Behemoth!
[LEVI giggles]
Ahh...
[LEVI cries]
Save the stomping for
Belphegor, not my bubble art!
[footsteps]
[door opens, closes]
[LUCIFER sighs]
[phone rings]
Mm? Get the phone!
Stop ringing!
[LUCIFER gasps]
Behemoth, huh?
[LUCIFER yells]
[BELPHE giggles] Wow. Rocking
your birthday suit today?
Can't blame you.
It's hard enough to get out of
bed, let alone put clothes on.
[LUCIFER]
We meet again, Belphegor.
I see you saved me the trouble
of hunting you down.
[BELPHE]
No prob, Lucy. Any time.
[LUCIFER] Call me Lucy again
and I'll yank that tail
straight off your ass. Anyway,
let's get this over with.
[BELPHE] Yeah, Belial is way
not cool with you. She told me
to stop you, so I guess that
means we're gonna have to fight.
I'm glad we're
on the same page.
[BELPHE]
Ahh... Mm...
That's great,
but instead of fighting,
why don't we play a game?
[LUCIFER]
What game?
[BELPHE]
My game, of course!
Mammy set up an
MMO RPG and I run it.
The idea is,
there's a demon lord
that tries to take over
the world, then, like,
a bunch of heroes come
together to stop them.
[LUCIFER]
Oh, yeah?
[BELPHE] So, you can be
the hero, or you can be the...
[LUCIFER]
Demon lord, obviously!
[BELPHE]
Uh-huh. Shoulda figured.
Then I'll start a
new event in the game
where the players have to team
up and beat Demon Lord Lucifer.
[LUCIFER] The players? I thought
I was supposed to be facing you.
Uh? But I have a ton
of subscribers,
and they're gonna wanna get
their money's worth, you know?
These "subscribers" are
your followers, I assume?
Oh, my god,
that's totally it!
They'll try to stop big, evil
Lucy from taking over the world.
If they lose, you can take
my seat as a Mortal Sin.
How about that?
Ah? Seems like you're
fairly confident.
[BELPHE]
And if you lose...
Do whatever you want with me.
That's not gonna happen, though.
Ah... Well, guess we'll see!
[LUCIFER yells]
[PLAYERS scream]
[BELPHE slurps]
Mmm...
[LUCIFER yells]
[LUCIFER] Out of my way,
weaklings!
[PLAYERS scream]
[BELPHE sighs]
Don't worry, guys, Belphegor's
here to lend you a hand.
[PLAYERS]
Our savior!
[BELPHE chuckles]
[BELPHE grunts]
[BELPHE]
You are like a demon!
On second thought,
we might have to recruit a
legendary hero for this one.
[indistinct chatter]
You guys hold down the fort
in the meantime. I'll be back!
And here I thought the game
was getting too easy!
We'll probably die a bunch, but
I bet the loot's gonna be epic!
[FEMALE SOLDIER B] Don't leave!
If you have to pee,
then do it in a soda bottle.
[MALE SOLDIER C] I'm totally
gonna livestream this raid!
I'm gonna be internet famous!
[MARIA] I think that's
everything.
[phone buzzes]
Why would Levi call me?
[MARIA yelps]
[MARIA gasps]
What happened?
Hello? Somebody answer, please!
Excuse me! Hey! Help!
[MARIA gasps]
What's with all this fog?
[MARIA] Maybe there was
no one out here after all.
[BELPHE]
Are you lost?
[MARIA gasps]
Uh-- Uh...
Pick that up for me, 'kay?
[BELPHE] Pretty light, huh?
That's cause it's a magic sword.
Yeah.
It has a low strength
requirement to equip.
And now, your armor!
[MARIA]
Ah--!
Try it on, girlfriend!
Looks like it'll fit.
[MARIA grunts]
[MARIA]
It's a little heavy...
[BELPHE] Let's try
it out in combat!
[MARIA]
Uh-- Wait, what?
Huh?
[DRAGON roars]
[MARIA screams]
[BELPHE] Mm! I knew that
armor was the right call.
Look, not a scratch on you!
Aah! I can't move!
[DRAGON roars]
[MARIA screams]
Stop it! This isn't funny!
Please, let me go!
Aah! Stupid lizard!
[MARIA screams]
[BELPHE giggles]
That's good enough for me!
[BELPHE]
This world needs your help.
A great and powerful demon lord
threatens to bring it to ruin!
[MARIA]
Demon lord?
Anyway, the details
don't really matter,
but the point is,
it's your problem now,
'cause you're
the legendary hero.
[MARIA yelps]
[MARIA]
I can't even... stand up.
Okay then, Plan B.
[MARIA yelps]
[BELPHE chuckles]
Shazam!
[BELPHE]
There! You like this better?
At least I can move...
But the back is really
riding up my, um...
[BELPHE]
Don't you play video games?
The skimpier the armor,
the better the defense!
[MARIA] How is that supposed
to make any sense?
Would you stop
complaining, girlfriend?
Take it for a spin and
you'll change your mind!
[MARIA]
Uh...
[MALE SOLDIER A]
We are so screwed!
[MALE SOLDIER B] No kidding!
Our "free-to-play" weapons suck!
[SOLDIERS scream]
[BELPHE] I bet you can totally
own that thing, Maririn!
"Maririn"?
Hold on, is that me?
I'm not strong enough to
save the world on my own.
Help me. You must become
the hero of legend and fight!
For great justice!
A hero? I could try...
[MARIA yells]
[MALE SOLDIER B]
Your DPS must be off the charts!
[FEMALE SOLDIER B]
That's a magic sword, huh?
What's your handle?
[MARIA]
The Hero Maririn.
[BELPHE] She's picking
this up pretty quick.
[BELIAL] I'm not much for video
games. Are we winning or not?
Getting there. I had
a minor setback,
'cause Lucifer stomped
all my players. But no biggie.
The Hero Maririn's got our back.
All according to the playbook.
She just has to level up.
[BELIAL] Very well.
I'll take your word.
[BELIAL] Just one thing. While
you're waiting on this "hero,"
could you straighten up
a bit? This is shameful.
But this is how I like it.
If I want a snack or something,
I don't even have to get up.
I can just grab it with my tail.
[BELIAL sighs]
[MARIA] Wait, why's
the demon lord here?
Well, why not?
Even demon lords enjoy a dip
in the hot spring sometimes.
If you say so.
Lucifer? Is that you?
What a surprise!
I get it! You're the hero
everyone's been waiting on.
I guess so... Never mind that!
This is awkward!
Why are you the bad guy
all of a sudden?
'Cause it's fun.
Isn't it obvious?
Stop complaining
and get over here.
A bath'll loosen you up.
[MARIA]
Not a chance.
It's cliché, but you can take
half the world if you join me.
No thanks!
[LUCIFER] You've
gotten awfully cocky
all of a sudden.
What happened?
The whole world
is counting on me.
I can't let them down when
they need a hero! I'm sorry!
Maririn, we love you!
Kick her ass!
[indistinct cheers]
Wow, you're quite the
celebrity, aren't you?
Can't say no to your fans!
En garde!
[MARIA] I'm gonna be a hero!
I'm gonna save the world!
Fine, have it your way!
I'll make this quick.
[MARIA gasps]
[MARIA yelps]
Do your research next time.
This place is the Chanel
Number Five hot springs.
You didn't read
the sign, did you?
Your lingerie
won't save you here!
[MARIA screams]
I can't do it.
I was so sure...
You really think you would
save the world if you beat me?
Whether I call myself
a demon or not,
I'm helping people here.
Wait and see.
[CAT]
Meow!
Meow! Okay,
that was fun,
but it would be lame if the
hero lost the fight already.
So why don't we just
make a hasty retreat!
[LUCIFER]
It's you...
Catch you on
the flipside, Lucy.
[CAT]
Meow!
[BELPHE] Okay, we're switching
you to plant panties.
[MARIA groans]
They're awfully itchy...
[BELPHE] I hear ya, but all
the plants in this jungle
are poisonous,
so whatcha gonna do?
[MARIA gasps]
I won't get sick, will I?
It's like they say--
whatever doesn't kill you
only makes you stronger!
You don't have any more
magic armor you can give me?
After last time? Nope,
now you gotta earn it.
And besides, if you can't
deal with some itchy panties,
how are you supposed
to beat a demon lord?
[MARIA] You're right,
Miss Kitty. Please...
Whatever it takes,
teach me to be a real hero!
[BELPHE] Alright, I'll school
you, but it's not gonna be easy.
The demon lord isn't
going to wait for us.
We gotta get you
into fighting shape.
That means it's time
for a training montage!
[MARIA grunts]
Okay, and punch!
Get ready! Go!
[BELPHE hums]
[hornets buzz]
'Kay, here we go.
[MARIA pants]
[MARIA]
Aah! I hate bugs!
[MARIA yelps]
[LIZARD roars]
[MARIA gasps]
[MARIA moans]
[BELPHE] In the cave behind the
waterfall of Julio Iglesias,
there is an angel who
controls the power of water.
She's the guardian of a
legendary piece of equipment.
[MARIA] Wait, so I'm
fighting angels now, too?
I don't know if I like that.
[BELPHE]
To protect the world,
sometimes you have to
do complicated things.
[MARIA]
Um. Hello there.
I've been waiting.
It must be the will of Heaven
that has brought you
here to me, mighty hero.
But before you reach your
destiny, you must face a trial.
[MARIA gasps]
Uh... Levi?
Indeed. I'm the angel,
Levi. Uh-- Ah--!
What in the hell are
you doing here, Maria?
You're an angel?
Shut your trap! I don't
wanna talk about it!
Why d'you have to ruin
everything for me?
Your angel wings are really
cute. You should keep them!
Forget the dumb trial, okay?
I'll just give you
the equipment.
[MARIA]
Are you sure?
As long as you leave.
Take it and get out.
One more thing.
Don't tell Lucifer about this.
[MARIA giggles]
It is cute, though.
If you say another word,
I will so put a curse on you!
[MARIA] This outfit looks just
like the one I had before...
[BELPHE] It's cheaper to do a
re-skin instead of a new design.
[MARIA gasps]
[MALE SOLDIER D gasps]
Ah! She totally came back!
She sure kept us waiting!
Just in time! Whew!
That's cool and all,
but I have to work
in an hour. I gotta log off.
Wow, is it that late?
[FEMALE SOLDIER 6B]
Shoot. I've got a test today.
[BELPHE]
Aw. You can't leave now!
[MARIA]
Ah-- Miss Kitty?
You're gonna miss the
big boss fight, you guys.
But I'll get fired if I take
any more time off from work.
[BELPHE] If your boss won't let
you have any fun, you should
just quit, right? Work is
for losers, I always say.
I'll give you some rare loot
if you stick around.
Whoa! This is Demon Gear!
We can take out the
demon lord for sure now!
Guess we can stick
around a bit, right?
[MALE SOLDIER C]
Dude, screw our jobs!
[LUCIFER laughs]
That's what I'm
talking about!
Destruction, panic,
chaos, running wild!
Once you've gone demon lord,
you can't go back!
But I still need more!
I need to strike an even greater
fear in your shaking hearts!
The Hero of Legend.
With your training complete,
you can vanquish the
demon lord at last.
[MARIA]
Mm.
[PLAYERS cheer]
I finally get
to kick some butt!
Your friend there really has
you on a short leash, Maririn.
You've got one last
chance to back out.
I won't listen to your
deceitful words, Demon Lord!
Fine by me, but I'm
gonna strip you bare
and leave you crying for
your mommy. Time to party!
[MARIA yells]
[MARIA yelps]
Just like before. You can't
keep your clothes on.
[MARIA gasps, moans]
I can tear them off all day!
[MARIA gasps]
That's some armor!
It's over!
[LUCIFER cries out]
[BELPHE] You did it!
Now finish her off!
[MARIA]
No, it's not right.
[PLAYERS cheer]
[MARIA]
Hm.
[MALE SOLDIER D] Okay,
seriously, going to work now.
[MALE SOLDIER A]
Me, too.
[FEMALE SOLDIER B]
Ugh, I stayed up all night.
This event was the best
one yet, Belphegor!
Catch you later!
Thanks for the loot!
It's not over! The story's
only got one ending
and she has to die. If you're
gonna be lame about it,
I'll finish her off myself.
[MARIA gasps]
[BELPHE]
So long, Lucifer!
[BELPHE grunts]
[MARIA screams]
You're being a real pain!
This is a video game--you need a
cooler special move than that!
Here, let me show you!
BELPHE wails]
The game isn't built for this--
you'll make the servers crash!
You think I even
know what that means?
I don't care about your rules--
I'm here to kick your ass!
[MARIA gasps]
[BELPHE gasps]
I was having fun
when this was easy,
but now you made everything
suck! Whatever! I give up!
[LUCIFER]
You admit defeat?
Everything's glitched out, I'm
gonna lose all my subscribers,
and it'll take forever to
fix this. So yeah, you win!
I'm never playing games
with you again! You cheat!
[BELIAL growls]
You were supposed to
be fighting Lucifer!
Yeah, but it was hard.
Games're s'posed to be fun.
I'm not gonna play
if it's a chore.
Huh?
Uh--! Awww, lame!
Glad you came to your senses,
instead of killing me.
I was afraid you'd
become another one
of Belphegor's
fantasy world followers.
That whole thing
was so crazy!
I really thought
I was a hero, too!
Even with the hornets
and the itchy plants
and naked stuff, I still
thought it was pretty fun.
I believed it until
the very end.
But when we fought,
it just seemed so fake.
Like part of a screenplay.
[LUCIFER] Of course.
It is a game, after all.
That means it's not really
possible to save the world.
Then what would the players do?
When one demon lord dies,
another one will take its place.
Sorry. I feel so dumb now.
[LUCIFER] Since you're
such a fancy hero now,
are you gonna fight me
and save the real world?
Or do you need your magic
lingerie to do that?
Uh! Would you
stop picking on me?
By the way, what's
the deal with her?
[MARIA]
Oh, uh...
[LUCIFER] Are those angel wings?
If you're trying to pick
a fight with me, Levi,
I'll be happy to oblige.
[LEVI]
I'm so dead...