[applause]
[ANNOUNCER]
Welcome to Gourmet Nouveau,
here in the heart of Paris, the
culinary capital of the world!
Our host tonight
in this feast of pleasures
is none other than Beelzebub,
the Queen of Gluttony!
[FOLLOWERS] We thank you for
this meal, Beelzebub.
Welcome one, welcome all, to a
feast you won't soon forget.
Together we shall eat to our
fill and celebrate the joys of--
[LUCIFER laughs]
What a joke.
Even for a demon, your party
is terribly low-class.
Don't you have any shame?
When it comes to pigs, I guess
they'll swallow anything.
Lu... Lucifer?
I'm sure my invite was lost in
the mail, so I just dropped by.
You know what I've been up
to lately, so I'll spare you
the whole backstory.
Let's cut straight to the chase.
I came here because
I want to fight.
Right now?
Don't look so scared,
I prefer to beat my opponents
at their own game, so to speak.
Since you've got the food
all laid out, I challenge you
to an eating contest!
But I... uh...
[ANNOUNCER] Did you hear that,
ladies and gentlemen?
What a rare opportunity!
Beelzebub is going to show us
the true meaning of gluttony!
No, wait...
[indistinct chatter]
[AUDIENCE] Beelzebub...
Beelzebub... Beelzebub...
[BEELZE whimpers]
[bell rings]
[indistinct chatter]
She sure is adorable,
isn't she? There's no contest.
I mean, when it comes to
eating too, of course. Ah--!
[LUCIFER]
Mmm...
She's really
savoring every bite!
When you're done
with that, eat me too!
I can think of plenty of places
your tongue would love!
[audience gasps]
What? You gain followers
by stealing their hearts.
Every demon lord knows that.
We're just eating,
aren't we?
Of course.
[LEVI giggles] Lucifer's
got this in the bag!
Let's hope.
[LUCIFER]
M-My stomach...
[MARIA]
What's wrong?
You can do it--
just hang in there!
[ANNOUNCER] With only
five minutes to spare,
Beelzebub gets a second wind!
Seems like slow and steady
wins the gourmet race as well!
Let's watch the master at work!
[LUCIFER groans]
I'm not done.
[LUCIFER]
Screw you, stomach.
[BEELZE belches]
--[bell rings]
--[applause]
[ANNOUNCER] Remarkable!
It seems it was a tie!
[BEELZE belches]
[LUCIFER groans]
[LUCIFER]
I gotta go.
Hey, wait!
Let's go!
[LUCIFER retches]
[LUCIFER] This is stupid!
What is going on here?
[LUCIFER] Ow... Why?
It's just food!
[BEELZE retches]
Oh, geez, not you too. Hasn't
there been enough puking today?
[LUCIFER gasps, moans]
You really like
to scare us, huh?
I'm glad you're awake!
Where am I? What's this?
What happened?
[LUCIFER]
Who the hell are you?
We took you to a hospital.
You don't remember passing
out in the bathroom?
Passing out? Mm...
[LUCIFER gasps]
How pathetic.
I just ate too much!
It's a bit more than that.
It appears that you're
suffering from a stomach flu.
A stomach flu?
I'm afraid we can't send
you back home just yet.
I have a number of
tests I'd like to run.
I need someone to fill out your
paperwork--a relative, perhaps?
Huh? Why me?
Because we don't know
any other humans here.
Fair enough.
Uh, yeah. I guess I'm
kinda like a relative.
In that case,
please come along.
You're doing her
a favor, trust me.
It's a whole stack
of documents.
You'll want to
sit down for this.
Sounds like fun.
[LUCIFER sighs]
[DOCTOR]
Maria Totsuka.
What exactly is your
relationship to the patient?
Well, uh...
It's complicated,
but we'll be stuck
together for a while.
[DOCTOR]
Oh, what a shame.
You mean...
I can't do this after all?
I'm not worried about the
papers--I'm worried about her.
Having the right person
by her side can be
even more important than having
the right doctor. Understand?
I think she'll be okay.
It's true, we do have kind
of a strange relationship,
but we get along pretty well
most of the time. And...
...she's pretty tough.
A little flu won't beat her.
Sorry, ma'am, but I need you
to take those big horns
out of your hair
before we get started.
You can see them?
[DOCTOR B]
Uh-huh...
Oh, actually, you can keep
them on. They're fine.
[MALE DOCTOR A]
Hm. This is weird.
It's showing two heartbeats.
That's not right.
[LUCIFER] These people
aren't helping.
They're just getting on my
nerves. I don't have enough
magic right now to stop
all their stupid questions.
[MARIA gasps]
You okay?
I can't believe I need
a human to help me walk.
It's nice.
For me, at least.
What? Nice how?
[MARIA laughs]
Never mind.
How did I end up like this?
What a mess.
[coughing]
[machines beep]
I'm crammed in here with all
these filthy, dying humans,
and this bed
is like a coffin!
It's a pain in the ass.
[snoring]
I'm used to partying all night.
You expect me to go to sleep
like somebody's grandmother?
[groaning]
Screw this!
Is there something wrong?
[LUCIFER] Yeah, everything!
How am I supposed to sleep
with all this noise? I asked for
a private room! What gives?
Sorry, but it's
doctor's orders.
What does that mean?
It's 'cause you're
a first-time patient.
It may be noisy,
but you're right next to
the nurse's station, so we're
here if you need anything.
[LUCIFER groans]
Whatever.
[snoring]
[LUCIFER sighs]
I wonder what Maria and Levi
are up to right now.
Actually, I like the time alone.
It's been way too long.
This isn't like me at all.
[snoring]
You're late! What could
possibly be more important
than coming to see me?
We couldn't get in before
visiting hours began
Excuses!
Here's a change of clothes
and a towel to wipe
yourself down with. I'll take
out your IV in just a second.
I'll clean you up, don't worry!
I can clean myself, Levi!
This stupid thing's in the way!
Lucifer, take it easy!
Stop treating me like a child!
It's just a stomach ache!
When you're done,
give me a call, okay?
Thanks, we'll just be a sec.
And off comes your top!
Here we go!
Aah! No! Why is
that so hot? Ow!
You're grumpy.
What's the deal?
"Grumpy"?
[MARIA] Did you
have a bad night?
You bet I did!
This bed is rock hard,
the pillow isn't fluffy, there's
no room to stretch, it's noisy,
I had to go to bed at nine,
the jackass next to me
wouldn't stop coughing, and
nobody would listen to me!
[LUCIFER groans]
Is your stomach hurting?
Everything's going to be
fine--just try to relax!
You're a million years too young
to be lecturing me, Maria.
Damn it.
I'm not lecturing you;
I'm worried!
[LUCIFER groans]
[MARIA]
Oh, hello.
Seems the intravenous
analgesic didn't work.
We'll try a suppository.
Wait. What's that?
[DOCTOR]
Turn over, please.
Uh... Um, no thanks.
[DOCTOR] Don't be
difficult, please.
What are you
doing back there?
[LUCIFER wails]
[DOCTOR]
Now stay still.
[LUCIFER]
I... I'm not ready for this.
[LUCIFER wails]
Butt stuff!
[LUCIFER screams]
[DOCTOR] Call me if
the pain doesn't go away.
You okay?
[LUCIFER] This is
worse than Hell.
I've hit rock bottom.
I have nothing.
[LEVI]
Hey, don't say that.
[LUCIFER] Leave me
to my shame. Go home.
But, uh...
Go away.
[LEVI] That was funny,
but I feel bad.
I'll find a way to cheer
her up somehow!
[DOCTOR] Look at that,
out cold already.
[BELIAL] You never had a clue
it was me, did you?
Like taking candy
from a baby. Pathetic.
My Seven Commandments must
have done quite a number
on your magic for
this to happen.
What's your true endgame?
What lies beyond
your petty revenge?
I'll draw those secrets
from your body itself.
Let thy flesh relinquish what
thy tongue keeps hidden.
[BELIAL chants]
[BELIAL chuckles]
My goodness, quite the
secret you had tucked away!
A heart? It's not yours.
Ah, must be that human girl's.
[LUCIFER groans]
Oh, no! It's gone!
Belial! Must be! Who else?
[MARIA] They said your
doctor quit all of a sudden.
[LUCIFER]
I see.
[LUCIFER] I was
far too careless.
Belial played me for a fool.
I doubt she knows the secret
of Maria's heart just yet,
but I'd better think of
a way to get it back soon.
In the meantime, let's hope
Maria doesn't find anything out.
[MARIA]
Lucifer. Are you okay?
Your stomach hurt?
[LUCIFER]
No, I'm fine.
You sure? If something's wrong,
we should call a nurse over.
Don't try to tough it out.
[LUCIFER] It's nothing.
I was just thinking.
It looks like you've got
a new neighbor moving in.
[LUCIFER]
Mm?
Anyway, I'll go have a chat
with the replacement doctor
and see if they need any
more tests. Levi should have
a change of panties for
you when she stops by.
Maria.
Uh-huh?
[LUCIFER sighs]
I'm sorry to impose on you like
this, for such a silly thing.
No big deal.
[LUCIFER] Although I guess
I'm imposing on you all time,
dragging you
into this mess.
[MARIA gasps]
You're acting weird.
Did they put you on a
new drug or something?
I was trying to say
"thank you"--is that so weird?
It sure is. I think all this
bed rest is hurting your pride,
but you'll be back to your
old self soon. I hope.
Ugh, gimme a break.
[LUCIFER] I just need to beat
the rest of the Mortal Sins.
My pride and her heart will take
care of themselves after that.
[NURSE] This medicine should
help your gastric dilation.
I don't think we'll
have to operate,
but I'm afraid you won't be
eating solids for a while.
[LUCIFER] Lot of stomach
problems going around.
[NURSE] Let me know if you
need anything, Miss Beelzebub.
[LUCIFER]
Hm? Beelzebub?
[BEELZE belches]
[LUCIFER]
That was one dangerous meal!
[LUCIFER] Come to think of it,
she was burping an awful lot
after the eating contest.
Even the Demon Lord of
Gluttony couldn't handle it!
I did good after all!
Hey, neighbor, you okay?
[BEELZE]
Um, yeah.
Tummy problems, huh?
I hear ya.
I got hit with a
nasty stomach flu.
[BEELZE] Then you
can't eat, either?
Not a bite! I haven't
eaten in days,
so I'm getting totally hangry.
[BEELZE] All I can
think about is food.
You must have one
heck of an appetite
to say that when your
belly is about to pop!
[BEELZE]
Food isn't the bad guy.
[LUCIFER]
Hm?
[BEELZE] Food makes you
smile when you're sad.
Food's a good friend
I can't wait to see again.
Can't argue there.
[LUCIFER chuckles]
Whoa! Lucifer!
[BEELZE belches]
[MARIA]
What's going on?
[LUCIFER laughs]
It's okay, guys, she's cool.
Turns out she comes
to this hospital a lot,
so she was sharing some
tips with me, right?
[BEELZE giggles]
[LEVI groans]
[LEVI] Nice that they finally
let you use the bath!
[LUCIFER]
I can do that myself.
Nuh-uh, the nurses said
that you need a bath buddy.
So I'm gonna scrub
every inch of you.
[LUCIFER moans]
[LUCIFER] My boobs are
clean enough now, I think.
[LEVI giggles]
You don't like it?
No, I really don't.
[LEVI] You only get to
have one demon girlfriend,
and that's me! I don't
like you getting all cozy
with that shrimp, Beelzebub!
You're making me angry!
[LEVI]
Too bad! I'm not letting go!
That's enough! What's gotten
into you? Maria, come help me!
If you don't like me,
then say so!
It's not fair! I give you
everything I've got,
but I don't get
anything from you!
Do you have any idea how
lonely that makes me feel?
Levi...
[LEVI]
This is all wrong.
Ever since you fell from
Heaven, I've been trying
my best to help, but now
I don't know what to do!
I'm dumb, okay? You have
to spell stuff out to me!
I don't think you
treat me very fairly,
but I don't want
to go back to Hell!
I want to stay with you!
I love you!
I know.
[LEVI]
Do you hate me?
Of course not.
Don't be ridiculous.
[LEVI]
You mean it?
[LUCIFER] Don't expect
this every night, okay?
[LEVI] Okay. I'm
so happy, though.
All my worries are melting away.
When're you gonna grow up?
[LEVI groans]
[LUCIFER] Ugh, gross!
You have got to be kidding me!
When I get out of here,
I'm gonna wring your neck!
I finally get to
eat some actual food,
and it's just some
crappy porridge?
Ahh! So yummy.
What? You like this?
When you haven't
eaten in forever,
the first bite is bliss.
Hello again, old friend.
I'm skeptical, but...
Mm! Actually, even if
the taste is bland,
the sensation is rather nice.
[BEELZE chuckles]
Ahh... I'd be a lot happier
if I had some meat.
It's good, though.
You don't want
something more?
What else do I need?
The porridge part is sweet,
but the side dishes it comes
with are salty. It's ecstasy.
[LUCIFER]
Huh. Let's see...
That is pretty good.
Told you!
I don't get it.
This is just porridge.
That's the whole point.
I'm really lost here.
Porridge is simple--
a little bland--
but that's why the other
flavors stand out.
Oh, I see. For someone who's
been robbed of flavor for days,
it feels so refreshing to have
them come back, one by one.
So, you finally get it, huh?
What makes you the Demon Lord
of Gluttony, though?
[BEELZE]
Hm?
Doesn't make sense to me.
A real glutton doesn't
appreciate the little things.
[BEELZE]
Aww...
And what? Do you have to go
to the hospital every time
you decide to binge on food?
If you're a demon lord,
shouldn't you have
magic to fix that?
I think it's fun.
At the hospital?
I got to make friends
with you, at least.
And the porridge is nice, too.
[LUCIFER]
Ah...
Quite the coincidence that
we were both discharged
from the hospital at
the exact same time.
I hope you didn't
have too bad a time.
[LUCIFER chuckles]
It's no vacation.
I do not approve of
this stupid arrangement!
What the hell is she doing here?
They must've planned
this together.
[LUCIFER]
Humans really are stupid.
They eat to live, but eat
too much and it's a sin?
That just makes you want to do
it more, though, doesn't it?
I love food, and I love
to share it, too.
I want people to be able
to eat to their fill.
[LUCIFER] Humans always turn it
into too much of a good thing.
[BEELZE]
I did too, at first.
But even if you eat and eat,
you'll never be satisfied
until you understand
what makes food special.
[LUCIFER]
Okay, let's dig in.
Smells great!
[BEELZE sniffs]
It's not a contest, right?
[LUCIFER]
More like a game.
I serve you the meat and you
have to savor every bite.
Simple enough?
[BEELZE]
Uh-huh. Sounds like fun.
Mmm...
You really know a thing
or two about meat, don't you?
I guess so.
[BEELZE] By the way,
you can have my throne in Hell.
I don't mind.
[MARIA gasps]
How am I supposed
to enjoy my meal
when they're
getting all cozy?
I don't need your throne.
When this is over with,
it'll all be meaningless,
you wait and see.
Today, we're celebrating
our good health.
Okay!
Here you go--say "ah"!
Ah--! More, more!
Okay, Bub. But just one
bite at a time, got it?
[BEELZE]
Mm...
[LEVI] Lucifer. Why are
you so cruel to me?
What does she mean
it'll be meaningless?
[BEELZE] Thanks for
the food, Lucifer.
[LUCIFER] I hope you like
the chain, too. Little Bub.
[BEELZE] Yeah. It goes
perfect with my collar.
You keep doing what you're doing
and let me handle
the complicated stuff.
[BEELZE]
Okay. I'll be waiting.
Ever hungry...
for your return to Hell.
[BEELZE giggles]
All right, ladies,
let's walk off those calories
while we plan our next move.
Come on, Levi.
Stop whining.
[LEVI]
Anything for you!
[MARIA gasps]
Oh, I didn't see you!
My friend is better now!
[MARIA]
What happened? I can't move!
No. It can't be...
What's up? Did she leave?
[LUCIFER]
Belial!