[MARIA]
It's an angel.
[LUCIFER grunts]
[BELIAL laughs]
Well, it looks like
I win in the end.
Heaven. I'm comin' home at last!
[BELIAL continues laughing]
You traitor, you!
Belial. How could you do this?
[BELIAL continues laughing]
[MICHAEL]
It's been a while, Lucifer.
[LUCIFER]
Michael.
At long last,
you're finally here.
Welcome, Michael!
Who are you, pray tell?
I am Satanael, the angel.
Do you not recognize me?
[MICHAEL] Belial, the Demon
Lord of Vanity.
[gasps]
As I promised I would,
I will surrender Hell
to your control.
--Damn you!
--Please be careful!
[BELIAL] Too long I have lived
in the fiery pits of Hell.
Now, I will return
to God's side,
where I've always belonged!
[MICHAEL] God does not make
deals with Demon Lords.
It's good that you
wish to do right by God.
Obeying is the solemn
duty of righteous creatures.
But one must not
expect remuneration.
All they had to do was tell you
they'd let you return to Heaven
if you helped with a coup,
and you joined right in.
I bet you didn't
even need convincing.
Belial, you're way too easy.
Anyone can see
right through you.
Did you seriously believe
God was planning to pardon
all your past
transgressions?
Please. I wouldn't be
surprised if God didn't know
about it in the first place.
They played you like a fiddle!
No, that can't be.
[ASTA]
Are you all right, Belial?
I think it's time to
end this bullshit.
What do you think Arch Angel?
[MICHAEL]
Loyalty.
[LUCIFER]
Hm! Well, well.
[MICHAEL] The Holy Light Wings.
The proof of credence and truth
granted by God to
the true leader of the
Seven Lively Virtues.
You lost these when you decided
to turn away from God.
[ANGELS shout]
[MICHAEL grunts]
[LUCIFER grunts]
[LUCIFER screams]
[MICHAEL]
Lucifer! You can still repent!
Turn yourself towards the light!
[LUCIFER]
Apologize? Whatever.
If you think I'll give up,
then you don't know me!
Lucifer, please!
[LUCIFER]
I've said what I have to say!
I'm not changing my mind!
[gasps]
[LUCIFER gasps, screams]
[MICHAEL]
I wanted to save you, Lucifer.
[LUCIFER] Is that a fact?
The way I remember it,
when it counted, you weren't
there for me at all, Michael.
You knew about God's errors,
didn't you?
Lucifer. I'm a loyal angel.
So you're going to accept God's
mistakes and do nothing?
God does not err.
[MARIA shouts]
Don't tell me you've abandoned
reason and logic entirely!
Hear me now. By order
of our omnipotent Lord,
I will now purge Hell of its
iniquities once and for all!
We will make a sacrifice
for the new world order.
[ALL gasp, shout]
[BELIAL]
Michael!
[gasps]
[BELIAL shouts]
[ASMO]
This is bad.
At this rate, I'm worried
Hell won't survive.
[MAMMON] We're gonna have to
take out Michael, and fast!
[BEELZE]
Alright. Let's fight!
I'm getting excited now!
[BELPHE]
I'm not, not even a little bit,
but I'll do my best to
keep a positive attitude.
[LUCIFER] Not so fast.
We can't underestimate Michael!
She is a worthy opponent.
Each "feather" of the
Light Wings has enough
vigor to rival the powers of all
Seven Lively Virtues combined!
[MAMMON gasps]
Yes, you're right.
Which means first things first:
we've got to do something
about those wings.
Gnosis. Now!
[GNOSIS growls]
By the honor of the
noble Byrnedale Family,
taste my vengeance.
[GNOSIS]
As you wish. Let it begin!
[BELIAL shouts]
[BELIAL]
I will have justice!
Michael!
[MICHAEL] There is
nothing more left to say.
[MICHAEL]
Hm!
The Byrndale House
is so famous,
there's no soul in Hell that
doesn't know its name.
As a daughter of that
illustrious house,
I am the most beautiful.
The most lovely by far!
[MICHAEL chuckles]
[BELIAL]
Hear me now, Angel! Mark me!
I am the Demon Lord Belial!
Michael, prepare yourself!
[MICHAEL shouts]
[BELIAL grunts]
Your proud wings of light.
At least I'll fall back
to Earth with one in hand.
[MICHAEL gasps]
[SATAN]
Lord Belial! Excellent work!
I guess it's true.
Anything's possible!
[ASMO gasps] Watching them
go to town made me all wet!
Just what I'd expect
from our former leader.
[BEELZE]
Mm-hm.
[BELIAL gasps]
[gasps]
What is it, Astaroth?
Darling, Belial. I'll follow
you anywhere you go!
Do as you wish, then.
[MARIA]
What is this?
Oh, wow.
It's over there, too!
Is that a statue?
[gasps]
O-O-Of me?
I think it's about time I
introduce the new leadership!
[LUCIFER] The Demon Lord
of Envy. Leviathan!
And the top dog? The Head of
the Seven Sins? Yours truly.
The great Demon Lord
of Pride. Lucifer!
[SATAN grunts]
Alright, Sins, let's do this.
Come at me and see how you fare.
[MAMMON grunts]
She's strong.
[ASMO] That's true.
But then again, so are we!
[BEELZE] Come on, everyone!
Keep fighting!
[SATAN]
Lord Belial showed us the way!
We just have to follow her lead!
[MICHAEL] I'll expel that fiery
passion of yours, Wrath!
[shouts] Oh, come on.
If you wanna take me down,
then you're gonna have
to do better than that!
Blade of Wrath! Howl for me!
Execution Purgatory Slice!
What?
[gasps]
[MICHAEL shouts]
Heh. Do you feel my rage?
Do you understand now?
[MICHAEL grunts]
[BELPHE] You're the final boss,
it's only standard that
everybody work together
to take you down.
[MICHAEL gasps]
Don't touch me!
[BELPHE giggles]
[BELPHE] Well, talk about
getting burned, huh?
[MICHAEL gasps]
[ASMO chuckles] Since you love
those light wings so much,
how about I pluck them
off of you one by one?
[MICHAEL gasps]
No! Stop it! Please don't!
[BEELZE]
It's time to eat.
[MICHAEL gasps]
[BEELZE grunts]
[screams]
[MICHAEL groans]
[ASMO gasps] I love those noises
you're making right now!
[gasps]
It's really hot!
[moans] You sure know how
to push my buttons!
[MICHAEL gasps]
Damn you all!
[ASMO shouts]
[BEELZE grunts]
[sighs] Taking this path
won't profit you one bit,
Demon Lord of Greed.
Why not walk away?
Well that depends on your
definition of profit, Angel.
Be eaten by darkness.
Return to dust.
[MAMMON gasps]
I'd rather not.
[MAMMON shouts]
What is this?!
[gasps]
[MICHAEL grunts]
Oh, no!
[MICHAEL gasps] My wings!
They're rotting away!
This can't be happening!
I'm done. I guess it's up to
you now. Finish it, Lucifer.
[LUCIFER] So? What do you think
of the power of the Deadly Sins?
You did well, but if you
really wanna win the day?
You'll have to beat me first!
Fine then. Let's dance.
Huh?
[MICHAEL]
Follow me!
[LUCIFER]
Wait!
[MICHAEL]
Lucifer, let's fight here,
with the whole
world on the line!
[LUCIFER scoffs] Fine by me.
Come and get me, Michael!
[LUCIFER, MICHAEL shout]
Look, they're right there!
[MARIA]
It's begun.
I'm overjoyed. You never fought
me head on, did you know that?
[LUCIFER, MICHAEL shout]
Yes, I did. Plenty of times!
You weren't serious back then.
[LUCIFER grunts]
It wasn't like this!
You never took me seriously,
not like I wanted you to!
What are you, stupid?
[MICHAEL] When you were sent
down, I thought of it like God
giving me one more chance
to prove my true worth.
Now that you mention it,
you were smiling, weren't you?
[MICHAEL] This time,
you'll take me seriously.
[LUCIFER, MICHAEL grunt]
[LEVI] Wait a second.
I think Michael likes her.
[MARIA]
Mm?
[LEVI] For a loyal angel,
God is everything.
That's why she's gone
weird like this.
[MICHAEL] Lucifer.
I'm happy. I feel great.
Cause at long last,
I'm fighting with you!
[LUCIFER] I feel great, too!
Because after I cut ties
with you, Angels, I saw what
real friendship looks like!
You lie!
[LUCIFER] Demon Lords who
say what they think and feel
are honest at least!
Unlike your kind, who will
say anything to please God!
[MICHAEL]
Hmph.
In the face of this tyranny,
you do as you're told!
You're just a fraud!
[MICHAEL] The foolish and
disgraceful humans will find
themselves in Hell
where they belong.
We will return everything to its
original chaos, and recreate the
Earth and Heavens
with a new world order.
This is God's will. Amen.
Are you fucking kidding me?
You created human kind.
Now you're just
going to sit back
and watch while
they're demolished?
And why, because they
won't behave?
You made this world!
Don't turn your back on it now!
My grace has reached its limits.
This is what God
has spoken, Lucifer.
[LUCIFER] Then stop obeying
and follow your own desires!
Oh, wow. I didn't realize.
I didn't know Lucifer
was the only one trying
to protect the human race.
[MARIA'S MOTHER]
Maria. Don't forget.
This angel is always watching
over us, no matter what happens.
Come what may, my darling.
She'll always be on our side.
What's that angels name?
Please tell me mama,
I want to know.
[MARIA'S MOTHER]
I'd be glad to.
[cars smashing]
[MARIA]
Mommy...
[LUCIFER grunts]
[MICHAEL chuckles]
[LUCIFER gasps]
This Holy Lance of Longinus was
made to destroy demon lords,
like you. Bye, Lucifer.
This is the end.
[LUCIFER groans]
[LEVI]
Lucifer!
[MARIA gasps]
[LEVI]
Lucifer!
[MARIA gasps]
[MARIA]
What's that Angel's name?
Please tell me, Mama,
I want to know!
[MARIA'S MOTHER]
I'd be glad to.
Lucifer!
If you hadn't turned
your back on God,
then we could've been together.
[LEVI]
Lucifer!
[MARIA] Demon lords can't die,
can they? Lucifer!
[MICHAEL]
Goodbye, Lucifer.
[LEVI, MARIA sob]
[MARIA] What do I need
to do for a Demon Lord
to hear my prayers, Levi?
[LEVI gasps]
Well, let's see.
You could make a
sacrifice for her, but...
[MARIA gasps]
In that case.
Demon Lord Lucifer,
I will sacrifice myself.
If only you will
come back to me.
That won't work.
You were always so
sure of yourself.
So arrogant, and over-confident.
But you can't even grant
me one single solitary wish?
You call yourself
a Demon Lord?!
[MARIA] Then come
back to life, Lucifer!
Please come back. Don't leave
me here alone like this.
Come back to me right now!
Maria?
[LUCIFER]
You know,
I think there's something
wrong with you.
I can't believe you offered
yourself as a sacrifice.
[MARIA] I can't explain it but,
I always had a feeling things
would turn out this way.
I guess I was enchanted by you.
Relax. I'm okay with this.
[LUCIFER gasps]
[LEVI]
Lucifer! Don't go!
[LUCIFER] Maria. I was
the one enchanted by you.
I've been watching you.
Ever since I was in Heaven.
You've always prayed to me.
During the good
times and the bad.
You'd always tell me what's
going on in your life.
And even though you talked
a little too much about
insignificant things,
I didn't mind terribly.
All I know is, I didn't want to
destroy the world you live in.
[LUCIFER] Maria. I swear to you,
I will use every ounce
of my power to put a
stop to this injustice!
[MICHAEL] Lucifer?
What did that fool human do?
Did she sacrifice her
own life for yours?
Yes, she did! Don't ever
look down on another human
just because you think
they're stupid, you hear me?
[LUCIFER] If the leader
comes back to life,
then so do the rest of
the Seven Mortal Sins.
Remember? That's how
Demon Lords work.
Take this!
[LUCIFER] That lance may
have been created to destroy
demon lords, but...
Maria sacrificed herself
to bring me back to
life again. So now?
It won't work on me!
[MICHAEL gasps]
What's this?
This isn't the
Lucifer that I know!
Who are you?
[LUCIFER shouts]
I am a fallen angel!
The leader of the
seven Mortal sins!
And I stand here before you,
blessed with another chance
at life through the gift
of the body of Maria!
[gasps] No, it can't be
a trinity! How's this possible?
She's absorbed all the power
from the other Deadly Sins!
[LUCIFER] It's what the humans
call a miracle, Michael.
After all, it's not like
God's the only one
that can make miracles happen.
I know Hell. I know Heaven.
They've both been my home!
And I want to overturn them.
So all can be free.
So that everything can
be as it was meant to be!
[BEELZE]
Tears of blood.
[MAMMON]
The sadness of Maria's death.
[SATAN]
Feelings of self-loathing.
[BELPHE]
And all forms of regret.
[ASMO]
That is what Lucy will destroy.
[LUCIFER]
This is her gift!
This is the miracle
Maria has created!
[MICHAEL gasps, screams]
Once again,
I've failed to succeed.
[grunts] So. Finish it.
Kill me. I want it to be you.
Prepare yourself.
It shall be so.
[MICHAEL sighs]
[gasps]
It's finished.
Michael. This time,
I will forgive your crimes.
You pity me? A terrible way
to say goodbye, Lucifer.
[LUCIFER gasps]
[LUCIFER]
The Seven Lively Virtues.
Get ready, because I'm
coming for you next!
Prepare yourselves for
a full on invasion!
[LEVI sobs]
I'm so torn up inside,
I honestly can't tell if I
should be happy you're back
or sad she's gone forever!
Maria...
[gasps]
[LEVI]
H-Huh? What's this?
[ALL}
Huh?
Maria, you're alive?
[MARIA gasps]
Where am I?
[gasps]
Oh, Lucifer. I saw
the entire thing.
Yeah?
[LEVI sobs]
Oh, Maria!
She's alive?
Maria's totally lucky Lucy
had some leftover angel blood
or she'd be pushing up daisies.
Do you really believe that's
how Maria came back to life?
Come on, Belph!
That's impossible!
[MAMMON] No, that's what
they'd call a miracle.
[SATAN]
One too many you ask me.
Well, at least it
was interesting.
Now that you brought Maria
back, does that mean there's
no more angel blood flowing
through your veins, Lucy?
Look, as far as I'm concerned,
I'm done with the angel stuff.
But Lucifer?
[LUCIFER]
Ya know why?
Well, I'll tell you.
'Cause I'm the best there is.
The leader of the
Seven Mortal Sins!
The Demon Lord
of Pride! Lucifer!
[ASTA] Oh, Belial.
It's time to eat.
[ASTA] Also, do me
a favor, will ya?
Come to my street
concert tonight!