[MARIA gasps]
I'm not an angel.
Not anymore, at least.
[LUCIFER chuckles]
[MARIA shudders]
This isn't fair.
I have to die for nothing?
It doesn't even hurt, does it?
Who says you're gonna die?
Wait. I can't feel
a thing. But why?
[LUCIFER] Here.
See for yourself.
[MARIA gasps]
[MARIA]
That's my heart...
That's right.
Did you miss the part
where I pulled it out
of your chest just now?
[MARIA]
The wound is healing.
[LUCIFER] Yep. Nice and tidy.
How about a "thank you"?
But how? None of this
makes any sense.
I can't live without a heart.
I must be dreaming.
Since you're so stupid,
I'll explain things.
Not only are you still alive--
as long as Lucifer here
has your heart, you'll
stay that way forever.
But if you wanna die,
I could help ya.
I'll just grab that
beating heart of yours
and squeeze it till there's
nothing left but a bloody pulp.
Y-You're awful! Stop it!
That's enough!
Give it back!
[LUCIFER]
Nope.
Why are you
doing this to me?
[MARIA groans, gasps]
[MARIA pants]
[LUCIFER chuckles]
[LEVI]
Wow. Badass.
So tell me, what are you gonna
do with a human girl's heart?
None of your business.
How about that?
Ahh! I wanna know...
I'm so pissed off.
I want a damn rematch.
I was outnumbered, that's all.
Those Mortal Sins have no idea
who they messed with.
I promise, I'm going
to show them
just how terrifying I can be...
next time we fight!
[SATAN] Now we know the strength
of the Seven Lively Virtues.
Or a fallen one, at least.
Looking to purchase
a new axe?
[ASMO moans]
[ASMO] I thought I'd finally get
to see what angel tastes like.
It's not fair!
[BELIAL] You saw
how amazing I was.
I made a fool out of
that arrogant angel.
Let's forget her and move on.
By the way Belial,
why are you still naked?
Are you too vain to admit that
she destroyed your clothes?
[BELIAL] I branded
that fallen angel
with the Garb of Punishment.
A secret weapon passed down
through generations of
the Byrnedale Family.
I have thoroughly
ensured her undoing.
Who cares if I happened
to do so in the nude?
That only means I'm not
dependent on my wardrobe
for success.
I should be proud.
Sounds like some revisionist
history, but what do I know?
She is the Sin of Vanity.
It's impossible for her
to see the truth when
it's not in her favor.
Well, Lucifer. I hope
you're crazy enough
to come back
for another battle.
[MARIA weeps]
[LUCIFER] Stop whining
and come with me.
[LEVI] Wait, what? We're taking
this stupid crybaby with us?
Uh-huh. Got a
problem with that?
I'd rather just put her
out of her misery.
Dinner is served, my friend!
[MARIA screams]
[WATER DRAGON roars]
[LEVI screams]
Am I not good enough for you?
I'm taking her with me and
that's all you need to know.
You don't have any
say in the matter.
But why? She's a human!
She'll only slow us down!
[LUCIFER] If she does, I can
always get rid of her later.
I won't drag you by your hair,
but I can't make any promises
about your heart if
you don't come along.
[MARIA gasps]
[LEVI] Is this our
new home? Sweet!
[MARIA]
Mm?
[faint chatter]
Seemed like the nicest place in
town, so I thought "why not"?
Hey, Maria. Hotel reservations
are a human thing, You do it.
[MARIA gasps]
Good evening, ma'am. Can I
get your name, please?
[MARIA]
Is this gonna work?
It's Totsuka. Maria Totsuka.
[RECEPTIONIST] I'll check
for your reservation.
[RECEPTIONIST]
There we are...
All right, everything
is in order.
According to our records,
it says you'll be staying
in the presidential suite
indefinitely, correct?
I guess so...
--[LUCIFER] Come on.
--[MARIA gasps]
[MARIA] What kind
of magic did she work?
[LEVI hums]
[LUCIFER] I suppose
this will do.
[MARIA] Whoa. I don't
know if I feel comfortable
spending the night here,
since I know
we're definitely
not paying for it.
"Spending the night"? This
penthouse belongs to you now.
It's your new home.
Wait, it's mine?
That's right.
For all eternity.
I don't need a
place like this.
I don't even know why
I'm here in the first place.
Why do you need me?
Stop asking questions.
It's not important.
[MARIA]
That's not fair.
You took my heart away.
Can't you at least tell me why?
What, this little thing?
[MARIA gasps]
It's not really your
heart anymore, is it?
You're cruel!
[LEVI]
Lucifer!
[LEVI giggles]
Come on!
Let's have some fun!
[LEVI moans]
So squishy and creamy--
agh, your tits are rockin'!
What did you expect?
--[LUCIFER moans]
--[LEVI giggles]
Sounds like I hit
the right spot.
[LUCIFER]
I'm gonna hit you.
--Lay off.
--No fair.
Why are you acting
like such a prude?
[LUCIFER] You need
to cool your jets.
[LEVI]
I can't with you around!
I got it!
[LUCIFER] You really want
that back, don't you?
What's the matter?
You don't trust a demon lord
to take care of your
heart? Come get it.
Afraid of a little water?
Uh, I'm okay, thank you.
[MARIA yelps, groans]
What are you doing?
C'mon, stop your
whimpering and get naked.
[MARIA] Ah... I'll swim in
my clothes; just let me go.
Who the hell goes swimming
with their clothes on?
That's bad manners,
if you ask me.
No, it's not!
[LUCIFER sighs]
Aah! No! Please, oh God!
I... I can't stop!
[MARIA shudders]
[MARIA]
I get it. That's enough!
[LEVI]
Aaah...!
[MARIA]
I'll do it myself...!
Oh, now you say that?
If you'd played nice
in the first place,
this wouldn't be an issue.
[MARIA squeals]
That wasn't so hard,
now, was it?
You're a demon.
You really are!
[LUCIFER]
Demon lord.
Ahh. You should make her
fly out a window instead,
so we can be alone!
[LEVI groans]
Bitch.
Maria. Come over here.
[LEVI]
She's ignoring me.
Lucifer!
Hey, look! Here!
I'll show you a cool trick.
Ta-da!
[LUCIFER laughs]
A whirlpool? This is fun!
Make it go faster.
[LEVI]
Sure! Anything for you!
[MARIA squeals]
You sure are helpless...
[MARIA coughs]
[LEVI] Just let her drown!
Why do you like her so much?
Who knows?
I do whatever I want.
[LEVI groans]
[LEVI]
This blows.
[MARIA]
I don't know...
I don't know why you
chose me, either.
Not this again.
If you don't need me,
then let me go!
[LUCIFER] Don't you realize
I'm doing you a favor?
Stop complaining and just
roll with it, all right?
"Roll with it"? Seriously?
Listen. You can't die anymore.
You won't grow old. You'll stay
young and beautiful just like
you are for all eternity.
Immortality. Isn't that
all you humans long for?
I was fine before! Turn me
back to normal. Please!
[LUCIFER] That's what you want?
To grow old and shriveled up?
Ravaged by age and disease?
Come back to me in 60 years and
see if you feel the same way.
Kidding. You don't get
to make that decision,
because I'm
the one in charge.
All you need to worry about
is following instructions.
[LEVI] She's ruining everything!
Pay attention to me, damn it!
[LEVI groans]
[LUCIFER] I want the best food
this world has to offer.
Let's see what they've got here.
Hmm. This sounds impressive.
"The Premium Dinner, Full Course
Special." Let's see if they
can satisfy me with their
primitive human cuisine.
Mm?
I'll cook for you.
If you really want to be
satisfied, then you need
a home-cooked meal
straight from Hell!
Just sit tight and let me
do my thing, 'kay?
[LEVI hums]
This'll be good.
Uh... I think I'll pass.
[LEVI gasps]
[LEVI growls]
[LUCIFER] What did
you do to me, Belial?
[LEVI] Luci-poo,
I'm so lonely without you.
I wonder where you ran off to.
Do you know
where she went?
[MARIA]
Uh, no.
[LEVI] She should've taken
me with her! What's the deal?
[MARIA]
By the way...
[LEVI]
Hmm?
It looked scary, but your
food was wonderful.
Mm... You weren't supposed
to eat any in the first place!
Just so we're clear, I hate
your guts! So I don't need
your compliments!
You're my worst enemy!
You're the one who's getting
between me and Lucifer!
I wish you were dead!
I wish I could kill you!
[MARIA squeals]
Please stop it.
[MARIA gasps]
I know she said
you're immortal,
but it might be fun
to try at least.
[MARIA]
Huh?
No!
You think Lucifer
would forgive me
if I ripped you to pieces
or filled you with holes?
[MARIA pants]
[MARIA sighs]
Why is this happening
to me? She's crazy.
[LEVI laughs]
[LEVI]
You sure look pathetic!
[MARIA gasps, squeals]
[MARIA]
No!
[MARIA squeals]
[LEVI]
I don't need to kill you.
I thought of something
even better. I'm going
to torment your sorry ass
until you wish you were dead!
[MARIA gasps]
[MARIA squeals]
[MARIA cries out]
Yes, that's it! You keep
screaming and moaning
like a little bitch
and I'll do the rest!
[MARIA]
This feels disgusting!
[MARIA pants]
[LEVI]
My goodness.
Sure would be humiliating if
someone saw you like this.
This is a busy hotel.
That someone could use this
elevator any minute now.
[bell rings]
[MARIA gasps]
[MAN]
Uh...?
[MARIA grunts, gasps]
[MAN]
Eh?
Why don't you scream
like you did a second ago,
so he knows what a
little freak you are?
Let me go!
[LEVI, MARIA moan]
[MARIA gasps]
[MARIA squeals]
Are you okay?
Ah! Uh... I'm fine.
Just a tickle, that's all.
[MAN]
I see.
You can't play this off
forever, you know.
I bet you'll feel better if
you let out a little moan.
Sure, he'll think you're
a perv, but who knows?
He might be into it.
Disgusting. I won't
let that happen.
[LEVI groans]
[MARIA whimpers]
[MARIA moans]
[LEVI giggles]
That one was pretty loud.
There's no way
he didn't hear you.
Pretty embarrassing, huh?
Ah... Why me?
Huh?
[MARIA]
What did I ever do to you?
[MAN gasps]
[LEVI] That's a nice
pose you've got there.
And he just turned around!
You really like to
put on a show, Maria!
[MARIA] It's not my fault.
I just want to be normal.
Too late for that now! Besides,
you were never "normal"
to begin with! There has
to be something about you
if you caught the attention
of a fallen angel!
I don't want
anyone's attention.
I don't care what
either of you do.
I just want to go
back to my home.
You don't have to do this.
I'm suffering enough.
[MARIA moans]
[LEVI] She chose you over anyone
and you can't even be happy?
You can't even appreciate it?
I would give anything
for what you have!
I'm boiling with envy!
It's consuming me!
Envy, and anger,
and contempt for you!
[MARIA moans]
[LEVI] I don't know
what else to do.
All I want is for her
to smile at me!
Why you?
Am I not good enough?
[LEVI, MINA] Is there
something wrong with me?
[MINA] I mean, I'm just as cute
as her and just as nice.
What am I missing?
I never thought I was the
jealous type, but jeez...
What can I do? It's not like
I can be somebody else.
It's nobody's fault, but I'm
gonna end up resenting her.
I don't know.
I've never had strong
feelings for anyone before.
[MARIA]
I'm jealous too.
It must be nice to have a
person who you love so much.
Are you crazy?
[MARIA] Maybe I'm just glad
that humans and demons aren't
so different. I don't think
there's anything wrong with
wanting something, and I don't
think there's anything wrong
with you for wanting it.
Even if it doesn't make sense.
You can't help...
who you are, right?
[LEVI gasps]
Why are you telling me this?
[MARIA] It'll work out
one way or another.
[LEVI gasps]
[MARIA] Instead of being
angry, just be yourself.
Stop it! Don't act
like we're the same!
Envy is a mortal sin!
Stop trying to justify it!
It's not a sin.
I think it's only human.
No! What are you saying?
I-I don't wanna hear this!
[LEVI squeals]
[LEVI] What's going on?
That was you this entire time?
[LUCIFER]
I think you lost this one.
[LUCIFER] You may be the
self-proclaimed Demon Lord
of Envy, but this human
had something to teach you
about the sin
you're so proud of.
Either way, I don't
want you laying
a finger on her again.
You understand?
[MARIA gasps]
[LEVI] If that's what
you want. I'm sorry.
It's fine. Maybe that
wasn't fun for you,
but I had a blast watching.
Finally awake, are you?
Feeling better now?
Yeah, I think so...
[LUCIFER] Good.
Then let me try this.
Whoa, hey, what are you doing?
Focus, okay? I need you
to find something for me.
[MARIA gasps, moans]
[MARIA]
I think I see something.
[LUCIFER] What is it, Maria?
Tell me. Where?
[MARIA gasps]
It's Miami!
All right, let's get moving!
What are we gonna do?
We're leaving.
To Miami?