[LUCIFER] Ugh. Man, this sucks.
If you're gonna kick me
out of Heaven, then at least
let me plead my case.
You're awfully petty, God.
Or maybe you're just senile.
You have been around
for all eternity...
What's that, God?
Can't hear me over the cheers
of all your righteous angels?
And screw you too, Michael.
I watched your back so
many times, and you stab me
in mine the first chance
you get. This is why
you'll always be second place,
you conniving little cheat.
Well, good riddance!
I'll fall to Earth, Hell,
or wherever it takes to get you
two-faced chumps out of my life!
[MARIA screams]
[MARIA gasps]
[MARIA] Um, hello?
You okay? Hello?
[LUCIFER] Uh...?
Wait. You can see me?
Yeah, of course I can.
Should I call someone?
[LUCIFER]
Strange...
What are you?
Not a human.
[MARIA]
Is that a joke?
[MARIA] I don't see any
injuries. That's good.
[LUCIFER] Over something like
this? Who do you think I am?
I need to get
you down somehow.
Hold on. I'll go find help.
Would you listen for a second?
I'm telling you, I'm an angel.
If you're human, you wouldn't
be able to see me.
But... I...
Give me a break.
Come over here.
Tell me your name.
Maria. Maria Totsuka.
[MARIA gasps]
Maria. You're very
blessed, aren't you?
[MARIA gasps]
What's that?
[MARIA gasps, squeals]
[LUCIFER] I'll entrust
an angel's life to you.
[LUCIFER]
Remember my promise.
Am I... dreaming?
[MINA]
Whoa, what happened?
Maria...?
[LEVI hums]
[LEVI sighs] When do I
get to be a Mortal Sin?
Cower before Leviathan,
the dark Lord of Envy!
Well, Behemoth? Was I cool?
No? Still need some work?
[LEVI giggles]
[BEHEMOTH squeaks]
Don't tease me.
I'm trying my best!
[LEVI] Uh-- Wait,
where are y'all going?
[LEVI gasps]
[LEVI grunts, yells]
[LEVI]
Seriously, what the heck?
Is that a cross? Oh, my gosh--
we got a real fallen angel!
[LEVI]
Whoa. It's gotta be.
That looks like Lucifer, too.
She's the triple crown!
That's number one in Heaven...
Number one I want to torment...
Number one I wanna see
in Hell! Here she is,
right on my doorstep, ready to
make my dreams come true!
Oh, great. So you
know who I am, huh?
[LEVI] Of course I do.
I'm your biggest fan!
[LUCIFER] Figures.
They hate my guts in Heaven,
but I'm some kind of
celebrity down here.
By the way, isn't it
kind of cold for Hell?
[LEVI] Oh, that's 'cause
this is Cocytus,
the lowest level
of the underworld.
Here, even someone as hot as you
gets frozen in no time flat.
[LUCIFER]
Yeah, I'm seeing that.
So much for stretching
my legs after a long trip.
[LEVI] Hold on.
I'll thaw you out. Hey, Whale!
[WHALE roars]
[LUCIFER gasps]
Aw, jeez. That's hot.
[LEVI] Mmm... The sweet
smell of searing flesh...
Her clothes melting
right off...
This is what hell is about!
You don't mind
the torment, do you?
There's an awful lot
of that down here,
but nothing an archangel
can't handle.
You can still scream
if you like, though.
[LUCIFER]
Tch.
[LEVI] Your skin is everything I
dreamed of. It's soft as silk.
Oh, I'm dripping with envy...
Stop it!
[LEVI sighs]
Sorry, but I can't resist!
You really should
put some clothes on!
[LUCIFER]
You're the one who--
Don't worry. I won't
let you get cold again.
Keep your tongue
to yourself, pervert!
[LEVI] I don't think you're
being very honest with yourself.
Why don't you let your
body do the talking?
[LEVI] That's right.
Open up and let me in.
[LUCIFER]
I said stop!
[LEVI] I've been a fan of yours
for a long, long time.
I think fate
brought us together.
Now, here's an idea!
What do you say we
conquer Hell together?
Then I can finally
be a Mortal Sin!
[LUCIFER]
Not interested.
[LEVI groans]
[LUCIFER] I'm not
interested in hearing you
run your mouth anymore, either.
I don't care about Heaven
or Hell or any of that crap.
I'm going to do whatever
I want from now on.
But what about me?
Who cares?
[LEVI yells, grunts]
[LEVI]
Okay, owie...
Y'know, I expected
some resistance
at first, but then
we'd kiss and make up
and you'd tell me how
awesome my evil plans are.
Then, you'd make
all my dreams come true,
'cause you're sweet like that,
but also a badass.
This isn't like
my fantasy at all!
If you think a little water
is going to hurt me,
you're even dumber
than you look!
Okay, you guys, attack!
Are all the demons down here
weak and useless like you?
Because this
doesn't even tickle.
That arrogance is
gonna be your downfall.
[LUCIFER gasps]
[MICHAEL] Your arrogance has
proven to be your downfall.
I'm afraid this is the end,
Archangel Lucifer.
God has spoken. You are
to be cast from Heaven.
Is that so?
Cast from Heaven?
Indeed. You must atone for your
sin of pride--for all eternity.
You shall never return
to these hallowed skies.
With that, I bid you farewell.
[LUCIFER] If you're going
to laugh, do it Michael.
[LUCIFER gasps]
[LUCIFER]
Go ahead! Do it!
[LUCIFER gasps]
[LEVI]
Ha ha!
Whoa! Awesome!
[LEVI] Beautiful, powerful--
you've got it all!
I can't hold back;
it's like a tidal wave!
[LEVI laughs]
You're so cool. I love you.
I don't even
know who you are.
I'm Levi, of course!
The demon lord who commands
all waters, Leviathan.
You and I are going places.
Just think of me as
your partner in crime.
[LUCIFER gasps]
[LEVI] I promise, you came
to the right place.
You're gonna stand on top
of all the Mortal Sins.
Make me yours and the rest
of Hell will follow.
[LEVI giggles]
You're lucky I haven't
put an end to you.
[LUCIFER gasps]
Ow! My hand!
Try that again
and I'll rip it off!
Aww... But intimacy is
important, you know.
But intimacy is
[LUCIFER] I heard you
the first time.
[LEVI] Yeah, but you were
supposed to give me a kiss
and say you were sorry.
Let's try again.
[LUCIFER]
I'm good, thanks.
[LEVI] This is Pandemonium.
It's the gathering place
of the Seven Mortal Sins,
who rule all of Hell.
[SATAN]
That's far enough, angel.
[LEVI] That's the Demon Lord
of Wrath, Satan.
Your kind isn't welcome in
the hall of the Mortal Sins.
I would start running,
if I were you.
[LUCIFER] I saw you peeping
on me earlier, but I suppose
you were too shy to say hello.
Isn't that cute?
You... You will pay
for your insolence!
[SATAN yells]
Well! You're quite
formidable for an angel!
You were able to dodge
my trusty axe... once.
[LUCIFER] Twice.
Your axe is slow.
Too bad.
You left yourself open!
What?
[SATAN screams]
[SATAN groans]
[SATAN grunts]
It looks like the
gang's all here!
[LUCIFER]
Hmm?
What a rare treat, seeing an
angel in our humble home.
Might I interest you in one
of my miraculous elixirs?
Aren't you cute? Would you
mind if I took a little taste?
I can show you pleasures
you've only dreamed of.
[BEELZEBUB giggles]
Okay, an angel.
Whatever. Don't care.
[SATAN groans]
These are the Mortal Sins
you keep talking about?
Mm. They're the seven rulers
who preside over all the other
demons in the underworld.
Looks like one is missing.
[MAMMON] Leviathan, dear.
It's fine if you want
to give your friend
as an offering,
but I must remind
you once again
that only the Seven Mortal Sins
are allowed in these halls.
You're gonna be the offering
when we're done here!
Things are gonna change!
'Cause I have her with me now!
[SATAN snarls] Fine.
I'll rip you both to shreds.
[BELIAL]
Quell your wrath, Satan.
[SATAN]
You can't stop me.
[BELIAL] Don't get
ahead of yourself.
If you've forgotten
who stands at the top
of the Mortal Sins,
I'd be happy to remind you.
Tell me instead.
Heh. You storm in,
you don't introduce yourself,
and you make
demands of me?
[LUCIFER] That's about
the gist of it, yes.
[BELIAL] I owe you
no explanation,
but I'll humor you
this once, I suppose.
I'm the daughter of
the Byrndale family.
Perhaps the most famous clan
in all the underworld.
You must be quite ignorant
not to recognize me.
My beauty is widely renown.
My elegance is legendary.
God! You talk a lot!
[BELIAL gasps] I was
just getting started!
Anyhow, that's the Demon Lord
of Vanity, Belial.
[BELIAL]
Argh! Let me say it!
Indeed, it is I. Greatest
of the Seven Mortal Sins.
Belial, feared and beloved!
If you have to toot
your own horn that much,
you can't be that great.
I know someone like you.
They had the audacity
to call themselves "God."
[BELIAL] Enough small talk.
Who are you, anyway?
[LEVI]
She's Lucifer! Duh!
This is Lucifer? The Archangel?
The leader of the Seven Virtues?
[LUCIFER sighs]
[BELIAL] My goodness,
how the lofty have fallen!
You must have made
a terrible blunder!
You can spare me your
fabricated explanation.
I've seen through
your deception.
This is merely a ploy
to invade our domain.
Heed my command,
Mortal Sins! Attack!
Mm... I see you're all
paralyzed with fear.
Very well, I shall show
you how this is done.
None is my equal. Face me,
and you will know defeat.
This might actually be fun!
Leviathan was the one
who dragged me here.
But I'm starting to think this
might have been my destiny.
Don't you?
The one that should rule the
Seven Mortal Sins... is me.
[MARIA]
Mm...!
[MINA] Maria, do you really
need another angel accessory?
Sure! I've been collecting
them since I was a kid!
Yeah, I know. I've heard
the story before.
Okay, but you believe
in angels, don't you?
I mean, that's what we're
taught, but I'd have to see one.
Like in person.
Then what?
[MINA] I dunno, I guess I'd say,
"What's up angel? I'm Mina!"
Or do you think they only
speak Latin or something?
[MARIA] She wouldn't
believe me if I told her.
[MINA] If angels exist, that
means demons are real, too huh?
The dark lord from ages past
shall rise again to
torment foolish humans!
[MARIA laughs] I don't think
that's how it goes, but okay.
Are you all right?
You've been weird since that
thing happened in the church.
Yeah. I'm feeling a bit odd.
Well, you're still
not as odd as me,
so I wouldn't worry too much.
Maria. If you wanna
talk, I'm here.
That means a lot to me. Thanks.
[MARIA] Maybe I was just
dreaming. I don't know.
[MARIA] Ah! Hey, uh, Mina...
What are you doing?
[MINA]
Sorry, but I can't resist
those child-bearing
hips of yours.
What I'm saying is, "Maria!
I want you to have my baby!"
[MARIA] Stop it--
that feels weird!
You truly are audacious.
Shall I expound upon the torment
you'll suffer at my hands?
Don't care.
If you think you can kick my
ass, then let's see you do it.
This is Dáinsleif,
demonic blade of my Byrndale.
Once it leaves its scabbard,
it will not return
until its foes
no longer draw breath!
Thousand Apocalypse!
[LEVI]
Aah!
[BELIAL grunts]
[BELIAL gasps]
[BELIAL] My precious
family heirloom,
shattered into
itty bitty pieces!
I hope the place you
bought it accepts returns.
[BELIAL growls] You rotten
little heavenspawn!
[BELIAL yelps, moans]
[BELIAL grunts]
[LUCIFER] Hmm. I thought
your sword was junk,
but your armor fell
apart even easier.
And by the way, even
if I came from Heaven,
I'm no longer an angel.
This is pretty underwhelming,
as far as spoils of war go.
To think that I would be forced
to suffer such an indignity!
I thought Belial
was all badass?
I believe she's
second to Satan,
like she's second
in everything else.
[BELPHEGOR] Uh-huh.
And you know what they say
about second place.
They're the first loser.
Very well. I suppose
I can lend a hand.
[BEELZEBUB chews]
[BEELZEBUB] One ass-beating
wasn't enough for you?
[SATAN grunts]
[GNOSIS] Pardon me,
my lady, may I speak?
You may.
[GNOSIS] It is I, your
faithful servant, Gnosis.
It pains me to see
you in such a state.
Please, use my body
as you see fit
and I vow to protect you
with all of my strength.
[BELIAL]
Very well.
[GNOSIS roars]
[GNOSIS growls]
[LUCIFER]
Uh--?
Fallen angel.
You shall suffer
for every insult
you have dealt me!
[LUCIFER gasps]
[LUCIFER groans]
Bye-bye.
[BELIAL] Heed your
leader, Mortal Sins!
Do not let Lucifer escape!
Use as much force as you like!
We can always piece
her together later.
[LUCIFER gasps]
[MAMMON] I suppose
I can give it a try!
[LUCIFER gasps]
[SATAN]
Get over here!
[LUCIFER]
Satan!
[SATAN]
We're not done!
[BELPHEGOR]
There you go.
[LUCIFER screams]
I wanna fight too.
Don't be greedy.
[BELPHEGOR]
Oopsie!
Ah! Asmo...
Such a perv.
--[LUCIFER gasps]
--[ASMO giggles]
[LUCIFER gasps]
Wow, I've never done it
with a fallen angel before.
By the way, I'm Asmodeus,
the Demon Lord of Lust.
I can't wait to hear all
your screams and moans!
Now is not the time!
Keep your grubby hands off her!
Besides, if Lucifer
wants to have sexy time,
then she should
have it with me!
[LUCIFER grunts]
No! No sexy time!
[BEELZEBUB]
All of you stop it!
--[clang]
--[LEVI groans]
--[ASMO groans]
--[clang]
--[LUCIFER groans]
It's over! Time to put you
in your place, fallen angel.
This is a land of
many torments,
and I shall give you
the full course!
[LUCIFER] You know, I get it.
The feeling of contempt
is mutual, but do you really
have to treat me like crap
just because of
the wings on my back?
I'm not too happy with
the angels myself right now.
[BELIAL]
Is that so?
Then I know just the thing.
It might hurt, though!
[LUCIFER cries out]
[LUCIFER pants]
[BELIAL] There's one left--
would you like to try?
I promise, it's quite fun!
No thanks. I kinda
lost my motivation.
You're sick.
I'm afraid that's a bit
violent for my tastes.
I'm fine with
fighting someone,
but when it comes to torture,
I'd rather pass.
[BELIAL chuckles]
Too bad. It's your loss.
You can cry if you'd like.
[LUCIFER]
In your dreams, bitch.
And just so you know,
this is only
the beginning
of your suffering.
I have all manners of
torture lined up for you!
[MAMMON] That's enough
for me, ladies.
Yeah, I'm done here.
[BEELZEBUB]
Uh-huh.
I dunno. I bet something
crazy's about to go down.
Hear my words, Mortal Sins!
[LUCIFER] I've now been freed
from my bonds to God.
You have my thanks.
I'll introduce myself
once more. I am Lucifer.
The demon lord cast to Hell
for the sin of pride.
[BELIAL gasps]
[ASMO] The passage from
this realm has opened.
[LEVI]
Take me with you!
[SATAN]
Is she being cast out?
Or is she intending
to go to Earth?
[BELIAL] Well, I hope
she learned her lesson.
I imagine it's the last
we'll see of her, either way.
I wouldn't say that.
She bears the horns of a true
demon lord now. You lost.
[BELIAL gasps, groans]
This is the last indignity!
Curse you, Lucifer!
[MINA] Bye, Maria.
I'm heading off.
[MINA sighs]
[MINA] Okay. Well, see you
next semester, I guess.
[MARIA gasps]
[MARIA gasps, yelps]
[LEVI] Lucifer, wake up!
Are you okay?
[MARIA] It's the fallen
angel from before.
You again, huh?
Who's she?
[LUCIFER]
Maria Totsuka.
I'm not an angel.
Not anymore, at least.
I'm a demon lord.