[bell rings twice]
[PEPPER screams]
[splash]
Hm. My masterpiece.
[LEVI] ♪ London, London,
we're gonna have some fun, ♪
♪ even though I hear this city
doesn't get a lot of sun. ♪
♪ London, London,
I'm here with Luci-poo ♪
♪ and I'm happy as can be,
even if there's work to do! ♪
[MARIA gasps]
That's so cool!
[LUCIFER]
Ah?
This is the best business
trip-slash-honeymoon ever.
It was much easier last time.
I'd hoped that searching a crowd
might give me some clues. I'm
not feeling anything, though.
[LUCIFER] Hey, Maria,
you want to fix this already?
Wake up!
Are you even listening?
Oh. Sorry!
Remember, we're only keeping
you alive 'cause you're useful.
Do your job or say your prayers!
Let's try harder.
Okay.
[MARIA] I almost thought I was
on vacation for a second there.
But nope. Still enslaved
by a fallen angel.
Still hunting down
demon lords for revenge.
A potion to make
your dreams come true?
That just sounds
like clickbait to me.
Nothing on the
internet is true!
Help us dig through these
newspapers instead, dummy!
[MARIA gasps]
How savvy!
She's advertising online.
You just got lucky!
Ugh, I hate you!
Let's get moving.
[MARIA]
Uh, b-- To where?
[LUCIFER]
The shop, of course.
[LEVI gasps]
We're gonna fight? Again?
But we just started
our honeymoon!
You sure it's open?
It's so dark in there.
[LUCIFER]
I'm going in.
[MARIA gasps] Did that door
just unlock all on its own?
[LUCIFER] Don't know,
don't care. It's open.
[LEVI] Get with
the program, Maria.
Keep sweating the small stuff
and you'll get left behind.
[LEVI] Is anybody home?
Doesn't seem like it.
We should come back later.
Lucifer, look. What's that?
[LUCIFER]
Mm...
A coin...
--No!
--Don't touch that!
[MARIA]
Huh?
Huh?! What happened?
[LEVI]
Ugh, you're so stupid!
Listen to your master's
warning next time!
How useless can you get?
Even a dog can follow commands!
Sorry, I didn't know. I just
assumed it was harmless!
Wow, useless
and sniveling!
[MAMMON] What a naughty girl!
You think you can steal
my hard-earned money,
just because I wasn't looking?
Oh, ew. Granny's getting all
pissy about her money again!
If you're giving us a lecture,
I'll just kill myself now.
What language! I daresay
you're the pissy one.
[LEVI] Ugh. Yeah, well,
I am stuck in a cage.
[MAMMON] Miss Lucifer, do you
have some business with me?
The Sin of Greed...
Mammon, right?
I've come to kick your ass.
How's that for business?
That seems terribly
unnecessary.
Why don't we sit down to a spot
of tea and talk instead?
[MARIA gasps]
No more cage?
[MAMMON] Of course not. I even
have some desserts back home.
Here.
[MARIA gasps]
[LUCIFER] I haven't
gotten to try many sweets
from the human realm yet. I'll
accept your generous offer.
What she said.
Uh, thank you very much.
[MARIA gasps]
You're not coming with us.
If things get ugly,
you'll just get in the way.
In that case,
you should stay too.
[LEVI]
Huh?
Just you and me.
Mm. All right.
Well, this is lame.
[MARIA gasps]
What's this place?
Just a little piece of
real estate I picked up.
I've been looking to lease it
out, but none is interested.
For the right price,
this could be your new home.
Would you like to
strike a deal, perhaps?
You really think I came here to
talk about leasing property?
I suppose not, but can
you blame me for trying?
I'm more about negotiation
than bloodthirsty revenge.
This place is stuffy. You
would've lost that fight too.
[LUCIFER yells]
You're far too weak to
defeat me in this state.
You just haven't realized it.
You think it's that easy
to get under my skin?
Confident! But if I win this,
I'm going to make you my slave.
[LUCIFER]
Just try it!
[MAMMON laughs]
[LUCIFER grunts]
[LUCIFER yells]
[MAMMON]
Too slow!
[LUCIFER yells]
--[sound of glass breaking]
--[MAMMON gasps]
[MAMMON] Agh! Do you
have any idea how much
that stained glass cost?
[MAMMON]
Tch...
Hey, Behemoth!
Time to wake up!
You don't have to pretend
to be a plushie anymore.
I need your help!
[BEHEMOTH squeaks]
[LEVI]
Ah...! You're the best.
[MARIA]
Thank you.
[LEVI] Ugh. If you really
wanted to thank me,
you'd stay in this cage
forever and die.
[LUCIFER groans]
I do hope you're comfortable.
You might be staying a while.
[LUCIFER groans]
Where did you take me?
Why does everything hurt?
[LUCIFER yells]
What the hell is this? Damn it!
[MAMMON]
It's your punishment.
[LUCIFER]
For challenging you?
[MAMMON laughs] No, silly.
You're being punished
for decreasing the
value of my property.
You think you've won this?
The fight's not over yet.
[LUCIFER groans]
Indeed, it won't be over
until you've paid me
everything in full.
Here's your invoice.
If you can't pay now,
there will be interest.
I'm not paying.
Oh, but you will,
one way or another.
[LUCIFER groans]
Think it over a bit.
[LUCIFER yells]
[LUCIFER groans]
I hope you're more
agreeable when I return.
I know that we're both immortal,
but I can be terribly impatient
when it comes to money.
I doubt you'll last long.
So that should come
as good news to you.
[LUCIFER groans, gasps]
No good. I can't sense her.
Help me look around for clues!
I'm trying, but I can't
find anything here at all.
What's that?
[MARIA]
Real estate papers?
[LEVI]
Here, give it to me!
Looks like a lot.
That's no surprise.
She's made money
selling property for
hundreds of years.
She took Lucifer to one
of these places. I know it.
You can sense that?
Of course! Well, kind of.
[MARIA]
But there's so many.
We'll have to check them all!
[MARIA]
That'll take forever!
I'm as tough as a demon lord.
I can do this!
If you're just going
to complain, though,
then leave already!
And don't come back!
[MARIA sighs]
[MARIA]
Another one?
This is a soul contract!
[MAMMON]
It seems that somebody
still hasn't learned
their lesson.
[MARIA gasps]
[MAMMON] If you agree
with all the details,
sign at the bottom here
and we're almost done.
[MARIA] What did she do?
I can't move.
All right, one more.
[MAMMON] Splendid.
Everything's in order now.
Here's your elixir,
as promised.
All I have to do is drink it?
That's right, dear, and all
of your dreams will come true.
After all this time.
Thank you, Mammon.
Good! Every last drop!
Now follow me this way,
if you would.
Right here. Step inside.
Of course. As you wish.
Now, you're next. We have a very
important matter to discuss.
I release your restraints.
[MARIA gasps]
I'm free?
[MAMMON] What exactly
is the relationship
between you and Lucifer?
Why would a human
accompany a fallen angel?
[MARIA]
Well, uh...
Should I tell her?
I can't tell how evil she is.
She seems reasonable enough.
It must be quite the secret
if you won't tell me.
[MARIA]
No. She's still a demon lord.
There's no telling what she's
hiding beneath that smile.
I think I understand now.
That must be awful.
[MARIA] Does she know
about my heart? How?
[MAMMON] Lucifer
slapped your hand away
to hide the truth from me,
but I figured it out.
[MARIA]
That's why she did it?
[MAMMON]
You're just a victim.
Lucifer took something precious
from you, didn't she?
But you don't have to worry
anymore. Come closer. Here.
[MARIA gasps]
It's all right. Don't be shy.
I can make you whole again.
I trust you. My worries
are melting away.
[MARIA] Somehow...
this feels right.
Good. Drink your fill of me.
Then, like the others,
you'll find joy in serving me.
You'll find peace in caring
for my dear children.
Not here. Better hurry.
[LEVI]
Ugh! Where are you?
[LUCIFER screams]
Was that her?
[LUCIFER pants, moans]
[LEVI gasps]
[LUCIFER moans]
Damn it! Aahh!
Don't worry--
I'll save you!
[LUCIFER moans]
Don't you dare help me!
If I can't do this on my own,
then all of this is pointless.
Are you sure?
Don't worry about me;
I'll be fine!
It's more important to
take care of Maria!
Not a chance!
I'm staying!
Mm...! I can't stop you.
But one thing, okay?
This is kind of embarrassing,
so would you quit
staring at me, please?
[BABY giggling]
[BABY laughing]
[BABY chuckling]
[BABY cooing]
[BABY giggling]
Uh-oh. This does not look good.
Did I go to Hell?
[LUCIFER] Agh!
Damn son of a bitch. Dammit!
[LUCIFER pants]
[LUCIFER wails]
Seems like she's
really suffering.
But all the moaning
and sweaty clothes
and hair clinging to her is
kinda hot. Actually, super hot.
I know envy is kind of my
thing, but I never thought
I'd be jealous of a stupid,
inanimate horse!
[LEVI groans]
I'm here!
If I can't save you,
I can at least suffer
by your side!
As long as we're together,
no pain is too great!
I won't let that horse
get the better of us!
[LEVI screams]
That... That hurts!
Stop moving!
[LEVI moans]
A-Aah! Get off of me. Moron!
[LUCIFER moans]
[indistinct baby noises]
What's that you're holding?
He's my sweet little boy. I have
to take special care of him.
There's no way that
thing is her child.
Listen.
You have to get out of here!
Those aren't your babies
you're holding! It's a trick!
[BABY cries]
I'm so sorry.
Please don't cry.
[BABY cries]
[MARIA]
Uh, there, there.
Good... boy? Girl?
Just be quiet, okay?
[MAMMON]
They asked for happiness
and that's exactly
what I gave them.
[BABY coos]
Mama...
[MAMMON chuckles]
See their smiles?
This is all they ever
needed in the whole world.
To offer up their love to these
children, for all eternity!
[MARIA]
Your children?
It's fine; they don't
know any better.
I've made them think they're
caring for their own children.
[MARIA] Why would you
do something like that?
[MAMMON]
For profit, of course.
I've taken all of their assets.
They don't need them anymore.
It was all in the contract.
Nothing shady about it.
[MARIA gasps]
[MARIA] That's what
those papers were!
Mm. My husband left me with
an unimaginable debt, you see.
As well as 500,000 children
I have to raise all on my own.
That requires a tremendous
amount of resources.
You cheated them!
[MAMMON]
The children are happy.
The mothers are happy
and I'm happy.
What else matters?
Now that you're here,
you'll be happy as well.
I refuse. This isn't right.
[MAMMON]
In what way?
[MARIA] I can't criticize you
for wanting the best
for your kids or for
trying to get out of debt.
But look! Your children
want their real mother!
[MAMMON]
Whatever for?
The human concept of
babysitting works just fine!
The mother might
feel that way, sure.
But what about the child?
This one was crying
until you showed up.
It knows who its mother is!
No one can take your place.
They need you!
What choice do I have?
I'm a working woman. I don't
have time for family, too.
[MARIA] I don't care if
you're a demon. A mother needs
to be with her children,
no matter what it takes!
Love will always find a way!
[BABIES cry]
What did you...
[LUCIFER screams]
[MARIA screams]
She overcame the
power of my milk!
[MARIA pants]
You have to let them go.
Even if it's tough,
there must be a better way.
You're asking me to break my
contract when they're happy?
[MARIA]
They seem happy.
But deep down, they're probably
just scared or running away
from something painful in
their life. Isn't that sad?
How is that my problem?
And what gives you
the right to decide
what they need,
especially when it's contrary
to their own wishes?
That's arrogance.
Foolish pride.
Did you say "pride"?
[LUCIFER]
You called?
Are you taking after me now?
Aren't you so cute?
Lucifer, you're okay!
Mammon. This fight is over.
Your torture room
barely slowed me down.
More unfounded pride!
All right, then. I can go
another round, if you like.
Of course!
I won't be satisfied
until I bleed you
for every last penny!
[MAMMON]
Ah! My shop!
Don't let it burn! You win.
This started with
a broken window;
it should end with one too.
[MAMMON]
No! Don't!
Augh! My money!
This is so lame. I finally
get alone time with Luci,
then she makes me rescue you.
Thank you, anyway.
Well, you did help me
find her, so I suppose
that's enough to spare
your life this time.
All my precious things!
[MAMMON groans]
I assume I won't
be needing this.
[indistinct chatter]
You're free.
[LEVI] Can we eat now?
I'm starving!
[LUCIFER] Maria, what's
famous around here?
[MARIA]
Fish and chips, I guess?
[LUCIFER] Mm... You think
that'll be good?
[MARIA]
Uh... I hope so.
Now Mammon has fallen?
I'm gonna strangle you, Lucifer!
[MAN] Your cryptocurrency
is catching on splendidly.
You were right again, milady.
[MAN 4A] The era of
the Mammoncoin has begun.
Heh. There's truly no end
to human greed, is there?
I'm grateful for that.
After all, I can't let
my children go hungry.
And they're just as
greedy as their mother.