[MICHAEL] How long
must you make me wait?
[MICHAEL] I was promised
the souls of the damned,
driven mad with corruption,
and I expect nothing less.
All in good time.
Surely you don't doubt me.
Now that I have seized
Lucifer's secret weapon,
there's precious little
that can stand in my way.
Come, let us seal
our pact at last.
[MICHAEL] Is that what
you're calling it?
Just hurry up. We don't
have long to finish this.
[BELIAL] Wrath, I have tempered
my expectations when it comes to
your intelligence,
but I had hoped you could at
least win a fight. For shame.
I have no regrets. I fought
with honor and lost fairly.
[BELIAL]
Hm.
[gasps]
[SATAN grunts]
[BELIAL]
What good is Honor?
I'm only interested in victory.
[SATAN screams]
[BELIAL] Am I to simply
pardon your failure?
I accept my defeat.
Do ask you will!
[BELIAL]
I shall!
[screams]
[BELIAL]
Lucifer's magic was weakened,
you should have finished her
instead of indulging in your
misguided sense of chivalry!
The Mortal Sins have allowed
themselves to become weak.
I am your leader.
[SATAN grunts]
[BELIAL] And yet all of you
choose to ignore
my expert guidance.
Tell me. Why is that?
Because you don't have faith
in anyone but yourself.
We don't trust you! Wake up!
If you want loyalty,
you should try to inspire it!
It's not about you!
[screams]
[BELIAL]
In my infinite mercy,
I shall grant you one last
opportunity to redeem yourself.
Simply perform your duty and
protect the Gates of Hell.
Hah. Lucifer will come
knocking soon, I'm sure.
And should you allow
her to pass through,
the gates themselves
will be your judge.
Consumed by its indignation,
your agony will be immortalized
in living stone,
for all eternity.
Right next to Lucifer herself.
[BELIAL chuckles]
[SATAN]
So be it.
[SATAN gasps]
[LEVI] Hey, if you're
gonna rescue Maria,
shouldn't you hurry?
[LUCIFER chuckles]
Just one last thing.
[LEVI gasps]
[LEVI]
Okay, I got all my stuff.
[LUCIFER]
What "stuff"?
[LEVI] Souvenirs from Earth
I'm bringing with me!
[LUCIFER]
Throw that crap out.
What?!
[GATES OF HELL] Through me you
pass into the city of woe.
Through me you pass
into eternal pain.
Through me among the
people lost for aye.
Before me things create
were none, save things Eternal.
And Eternal, shall I endure.
All hope abandon
ye who enter here.
[SATAN gasps]
[SATAN] I will honor my promise.
Hear me, Gates of Hell! Open!
I've given my command. Now obey!
[SOULS OF THE DAMNED groan]
[SATAN]
You will not defy me!
[MARIA shouts]
[BELIAL chuckles]
[MARIA whimpers]
[MARIA shouts]
[SOULS OF THE DAMNED groan]
[footsteps]
[SATAN gasps]
[LUCIFER chuckles]
[MALE SOLDIER A]
I've got you in my sights.
There's gonna be nothing left
but atom dust when I'm done
with you!
Oooh, scary.
[MALE SOLDIER A]
I'm goin' home a hero!
I like the way you think,
little man.
It doesn't matter what you do,
so long as you win.
Is that the plan?
I'd call that pride.
[MALE SOLDIER A laughs]
Suck it!
[MALE SOLDIER A]
Wait, what?
[LUCIFER chuckles]
And speaking of prideful,
you really thought you
could defeat me with
this little pea shooter?
You'll most certainly
make a fine follower.
[FEMALE JUDGE A]
Guilty.
I hereby sentence you
to the death penalty.
[FEMALE JUDGE A gasps]
What is this?
[LUCIFER chuckles] What gives
you the right to judge someone?
To murder them?
Is "justice" an absolute
that you alone decide?
My duty is to ensure that the
law is carried out properly,
regardless of what
conclusion it brings.
I have made no mistake.
So, "the law" gives you
the right to play God?
Justice can never be
burdened with doubt!
Here, in the court of law,
the judge is God!
Isn't that handy!
But I'm the judge now.
And I happen to find you
guilty of pride, that is.
[FEMALE BEACHGOERS chatter]
[LUCIFER] You came here
just to show off your body.
You're sizing each
other up. Pathetic.
You can party here until
Asmodeus makes you kiss her
feet again, or you can come
with me, and keep your pride.
Say it with me! Melancholy!
[CROWD]
Melancholy!
[FEMALE SINGER A]
I think it's time for me
to drop some rhymes!
[LUCIFER] You're nothing
but a second-rate rip-off,
I bet you can't even sing.
You think you're so cute
you can get away with this?
How prideful!
And you all know you're
supporting a no-talent hack.
But you have too much
pride to admit that!
[LUCIFER]
Next up.
The producers,
so proud of yourselves for
thinking up this cash-grab.
You're mine.
[LEVI]
Whoa! I can't believe it.
You've gathered a whole army
of followers in no time at all!
[LUCIFER] Humans care about
themselves more than
anything else. That means
they're all guilty of pride.
Every human is born with that
arrogance in their heart.
That's why pride is
the sin that rules all.
In fact, I could condemn
all of humanity to Hell
if I saw fit to.
Can you imagine that?
Not a single, miserable soul
making it to heaven?
God knows this, and that's
why they fear me.
[GATES OF HELL ]
One million. Ten million.
One hundred million followers
you bring to these gates.
You may pass.
Make way for the Demon Lord!
[SATAN grunts]
You kept your word.
Thank you, Satan.
'Course I did. But still.
I didn't expect you to come
with an army of followers.
This is my underworld
comeback tour.
I couldn't show up
empty-handed, right?
[SATAN chuckles]
That works for me.
[SATAN] The Demon Lord of Pride
has come to claim her throne!
[LUCIFER]
This must be Acheron.
There's supposed to be
a ferry waiting here.
We don't have time to sit
on our asses. Let's move.
[LEVI]
Uh, right.
What is up with this water?
I can't use my powers!
I can't even swim!
I'm gonna drown!
Lucifer, help!
[gasps]
Huh... Uh...
[LUCIFER]
And here's our ferry.
It's Charon.
[LUCIFER gasps]
[CHARON roars]
[BELIAL] I'm not pointing
fingers, but let's discuss
strategy to avoid any
further disappointments.
[MAMMON] Any reason
why Satan is missing?
[BELIAL]
Evidently, her loyalties now lie
with that fallen angel.
[BEELZE] I knew Lucifer
would keep her word!
[BELPHE]
Wow, you're killin' it, Lucy.
[ASMO] Just let her come,
Belial. It'll be fun.
[ASTA chuckles]
Enough of your sass!
You must perform your
duty as the Mortal Sins!
Go and confront Lucifer.
Strike the bitch down!
Heed my commands and this time,
we shall be victorious!
[SATAN]
It's too late for that.
[BELIAL gasps]
Lucifer has bested us fairly,
one after another.
Now, she returns as a true Demon
Lord, followers at her side.
[SATAN] We have no need
for you anymore, Belial.
You may do as you please, but
you will do it without my aid.
Farewell.
[MAMMON] Consider our business
arrangement terminated.
Good day!
[BELIAL]
Degenerates, all of them.
[gasps]
[ASTA]
Maria? A living human, in Hell?
[BELIAL] She's my ace in
the hole, so to speak.
[ASTA gasps]
[BELIAL] I
assure you, Melancholy,
if you stay at my side, you will
see a most wondrous chain of
events that will turn this world
upside down and put us on top.
[ASTA sighs]
I owe you my life, Belial.
Wherever you go, I'll follow.
To the bitter end, if need be.
Now, little ladies, I believe
it's time you pay the toll.
What? Y'mean it's not free?
[LUCIFER grunts]
[CHARON] I'm the only one who
can ferry you across this river.
I deserve a little something,
wouldn't you say?
[LUCIFER]
Like what?
Oh, not much. Just perhaps
some of those delicious souls
you brought along.
The bikini babe ones!
[LUCIFER] I don't think so.
I need those.
Well, this old-timer has
to get his jollies somehow,
so why don't you give me a peek
at your panties, pretty please?
[LEVI]
Creep!
[LUCIFER] I'm always happy
to amuse a panty fan.
But, if I show you,
I'll feel like you won.
Yeah, you tell him!
You stupid pervy boat man.
Just die already!
[CHARON laughs]
[CHARON] Ooh, licky licky licky,
my spit is nice and sticky!
[LUCIFER gasps]
[laughs]
A pleasant flavor,
with no aftertaste,
but a bit too mild
if you ask me.
I need something more than that.
I'm getting' licky with it!
[LUCIFER grunts]
The hell you are!
What is that awful smell?
Don't let him beat you!
[CHARON laughs]
Most young ladies pass out
when they get a
whiff of my musk!
You're a pain in the ass!
[LUCIFER grunts]
[CHARON]
Licky licky!
[LUCIFER groans]
[LUCIFER]
Screw this!
[LUCIFER] You saw your panties,
now lay off, you old freak!
[CHARON groans]
[CHARON]
Just kidding.
Even for Hell,
this is getting weird.
Now I have an excuse
to rip you to shreds!
[LUCIFER grunts]
You're a feisty one,
aren't you, little lady?
But I've got plenty of tricks!
[LUCIFER gasps]
[CHARON giggles]
[CHARON]
Licky time!
[LUCIFER shouts]
--[CHARON chuckles]
--[LUCIFER shouts]
[CHARON]
You like it? You like it?
--[CHARON chuckles]
--[LUCIFER shouts]
[CHARON laughs] This is a
full-service ferry, missy,
you should be thrilled.
[LUCIFER]
You wish.
[CHARON] Hm? I may not
be much of a looker,
but experience counts
for something, don't it?
Let her go!
I'm the only one who gets
to have tongue-time
with Lucifer, asshole!
[CHARON]
Yeah? Yeah? Yeah? Ha, ha, ha!
Somebody stop me!
You suck, old man!
[LEVI whimpers]
Let us go!
[CHARON]
Hot! Hot! Hot! Hot! Hot! Hot!
[LUCIFER gasps]
Nice job, Levi.
[LEVI chuckles]
I accept kisses as payment.
[WHALE roars]
[CHARON] We were having
a moment, damn it!
Now, get out of my way!
[CHARON]
And stay down!
[CHARON yelps]
[LEVI]
The souls of the dead.
[LUCIFER] Figures. They must
hate him as much as we do.
[LEVI] It's not enough.
I'll go finish him off.
[CHARON] Panties! I can
die without regret!
[CHARON groans]
Whew! That was fun!
The part where I kicked
his ass, at least.
[LUCIFER]
Yeah. Good work.
I feel bad for
your whale, though.
Guess that's it for him.
[LEVI]
Whatever.
There's a like a bazillion more
Whales where he came from.
More importantly. I'll take
my kiss now, please!
[LUCIFER] Sorry, we're here.
Business first.
[LEVI]
C'mon, don't be stingy!
[MAMMON] You surprised me!
All those followers!
It was quite the
triumphant return!
And we won't be
missing Charon, either.
Hey there! Haven't seen you in
a while, you're looking good!
Can you hurry, please?
Just conquer Hell or whatever
so I can get some sleep.
You made it! I'm so glad!
[LUCIFER chuckles]
[LEVI whimpers]
First things first. We need
to know what your plan is.
[BELPHE]
Depending on what it is,
we might end up fighting again.
Are you here to destroy Hell?
[LUCIFER] Not me, no,
but that's what God wants.
[ALL]
Hm?
[LUCIFER] The Seven Lively
Virtues received a decree
from God to purge
both Hell and Earth.
It won't be long now.
And what is your part in this?
[ASMO] Something tells me your
plan's gonna be pretty crazy.
Defeat God.
Flip Heaven and Hell,
and create a
new world order.
[BELPHE] Ooh! You like
to think big, don't you?
[LUCIFER]
God is a sore loser.
They're being childish because
no matter how much mankind
learns and grows, they always
find new ways to sin.
Humans help Hell flourish,
but Heaven, not so much.
I got sick of the whole
song and dance myself,
but God didn't like it
when I pointed that out.
Does Lord Belial
know about this?
[LUCIFER]
You bet she does.
[ASTA gasps]
If you don't trust me, by all
means, just ask her yourself.
[BELPHE]
Nah, it's cool.
[MAMMON]
I'm done with her.
Me too.
[ASMO]
That settles it.
[ASTA gasps]
We will protect Hell.
That's our duty.
[LUCIFER grunts]
Why does she get
all the cuddles?
[ASTA]
Belial.
Still siding with her?
[ASTA grunts]
She wouldn't lie to me.
I don't want to be enemies
with you, but I trust Belial!
[ASTA gasps] Uh, hey. You guys?
I'm standing right here.
Wow, you sure
are stupid, aren't you?
Belial is obviously full
of crap, you dummy!
[LEVI grunts]
[ASTA sighs]
Don't worry.
I'll take care of
this one for you.
Why, thank you, Levi.
[LEVI gasps]
[LUCIFER]
Why, thank you, Levi.
Thank you, Levi.
You're the only one for me.
In fact, when we're done
saving the world together,
I think we should get married.
Then have the hottest,
wildest honeymoon ever!
[LEVI gasps]
[LEVI]
Hold on a sec!
[LUCIFER gasps]
[LEVI] You better not cheat
on me while I'm gone!
You're all mine!
[LEVI]
Keep an eye on her, Behemoth!
I'm counting on you!
She always was
the jealous type.
[LUCIFER]
Better finish that fight quick,
or I might make
out with someone!
Why do you have to
tease me, you big meanie!
Let's make this quick Astaroth,
I don't have time
to screw around!
Well, tough luck.
[LEVI shouts]