[MARIA gasps]
Stop flippin' out.
It's just an airplane.
You really think
they're in Miami?
[LUCIFER]
Well, one of them is.
Asmodeus,
the Mortal Sin of Lust.
Wow. You could tell all that?
[MARIA gasps]
I thought we'd wait, but okay.
If you just have to look
at boobs on the plane,
look at mine.
They're way more awesome
than hers anyway.
[LUCIFER] Yeah, but your boobs
don't have psychic powers.
[LEVI groans]
[LEVI]
They don't look that special.
[LEVI grunts]
She has my blood
flowing through her body.
Or rather, the blood I had
when I was an angel.
[LUCIFER] I passed it on
before it became corrupt.
We can use it to find
the Mortal Sins.
[LEVI] Speaking of useful,
we'd be in Miami already
if we used my powers
to get there.
Yes, but I'd rather take my time
and enjoy the human world.
How insensitive of me!
I should've thought of that,
with this being our
honeymoon and all!
[MARIA sighs]
[car engine runs]
[LEVI] Why does this car
have to be so loud?
Did you find anything, Maria?
It looks like there's people
who won't leave the beach
for some reason.
It's all over the news.
[LUCIFER]
Well, that sounds like a lead.
You can be quite helpful
when you want to be!
How do you know it's
a demon lord, though?
[LUCIFER] If people are
acting strangely, it's likely
because Asmodeus is here
collecting followers.
Once they're drawn in
by her seduction,
their souls are forfeit and
they go to Hell when they die.
[MARIA]
That's awful.
[LUCIFER] I don't think they're
deserving of your sympathy.
If a human is weak-willed,
they have no one to
blame but themselves.
Anyway, if you don't like
what she's doing, that's fine.
She is our enemy,
and I need your help.
When you're done taking revenge,
I can have my heart back, right?
[indistinct chatter]
[WOMAN A chuckles]
[MAN, WOMAN gasp]
[ASMO chuckles]
[excited chatter, cheers]
[ASMO giggles]
[WOMAN B]
Look, it's Asmodeus!
[excited chatter]
Whoa. She is hot.
[WOMAN A groans]
My goodness. Everyone
is staring at me
with lust in their eyes.
Whatever shall I do?
[ASMO chuckles]
[MARIA]
We're buying swimsuits?
[LEVI] What else are we gonna
wear to the beach, stupid?
I bet Lucifer would take
everyone's breath away
with this one!
Oh, but wait...
That means I'd have to share her
with a bunch of lame-ass humans.
Can't have that, right?
But if she's wearing my swimsuit
that I picked out,
that means she loves me best!
I picked this out
for you, Maria.
Now try it on to
make sure it fits.
[MARIA]
Oh, no, thank you.
You wanna fight?
[MARIA sighs]
It's tight. And isn't this
like a sports uniform?
[LUCIFER]
Are you done yet?
[MARIA]
I think I'll pass after all.
[LUCIFER]
Not happening.
[LEVI] You're gonna
poke someone's eye out
with those nobby nipples.
[MARIA]
Ah...!
[LUCIFER]
Let's get moving.
[excited chatter]
[ASMO laughs]
It's a nice start, but I still
don't think you're horny enough.
Let the sand swallow you up!
Fall into the deepest
depths of depravity!
Don't hold anything back.
If it feels this good,
it can't possibly be bad! Hm!
[ASMO gasps]
[screams, chatter]
[WOMAN C]
Whoa, is she crazy?
[indistinct chatter]
[LUCIFER] Well, you
were easy enough to find.
Did you miss me,
Asmodeus?
Just a bit. You did take off
before we could have
any playtime. Have you come
to kiss and make up?
[LUCIFER]
I've come for revenge.
[ASMO] That's a good one!
I'm glad to see
that literally having your ass
kicked to Hell and back
hasn't spoiled your
sense of humor.
No, but I'll save my laughs
until after I've humiliated you.
I'm busy gathering followers.
Stay out of my way.
We can play later.
[LUCIFER laughs]
These "followers" aren't nearly
as loyal as you think they are.
Hm.
[excited chatter]
That wasn't so difficult.
Even Maria could turn
that many heads.
[MARIA squeals]
[LEVI] Showing off your nipples
again, you little perv?
It's not my fault!
[ASMO chuckles]
[MARIA whimpers]
C'mon, that's amateur stuff.
I was just getting warmed up.
[yells and cheers]
[ASMO] Young or old,
male or female,
everyone's gaze is drawn to me,
their lewd thoughts wrapping
around every inch of my body.
Beat that!
There's more to
the art of seduction
than just showing off your tits.
How 'bout the art
of kicking your ass?
C'mon, guys, it's time to go!
Why is this happening to me?
[LEVI giggles]
Did you forget that
I can control water?
The beach is my home turf!
If you wanna flee in terror,
now's your last chance.
Well, that's no good at all.
This isn't a place for fighting;
it's a place for love.
A place where people are going
to be making love, too.
[ASMO groans]
I can't have you
ruining the mood!
You will not be crashing my orgy
with a bunch of icky snails!
Ah! I can't hold it back
any longer--here it comes!
[ASMO moans]
[ASMO]
Pheromone Wind!
[ASMO chuckles]
[ASMO]
Maybe I overdid it a bit.
[LEVI] How dare you
do that to my Snaiba?!
[LEVI] Let me
handle this, please!
Even with the ocean here,
she still has the advantage.
She's drawing power from all
the humans lusting after her.
[LEVI] Then what are
we supposed to do?
[LUCIFER]
Just follow my lead.
[LEVI] Okay! If anyone
can win, it's you!
Thanks, but we're
retreating.
[LEVI]
Hold on. What?
[LUCIFER]
C'mon, Maria, let's go.
[LEVI] Ahh! No fair! I wanna
be carried in your arms too!
"Maria"?
[LUCIFER] This is where you
saw the vision of Asmodeus?
And she was gathering followers?
[MARIA] Yeah, that's
what it seemed like.
[LEVI] Let me take revenge!
I promise I won't lose!
No way.
[LEVI groans]
I hate this!
[LUCIFER] By the way,
what the hell are you wearing?
[LEVI]
I'm a mermaid! It's adorable!
Aw, I thought you'd
like it for sure.
[indistinct chatter]
I can feel her magic;
it's all over the place!
Better prepare yourself.
[chatter]
There she is! It's about time!
Asmodeus!
[chatter continues]
[LUCIFER]
Just watch for now.
[chatter continues]
[ASMO laughs]
You guys are so
naughty, aren't you?
But that's okay--it's cute.
Give yourselves up to me!
Let it all out!
Huh. She's gathering
followers day and night.
I have to admire her work ethic.
What's with that face, Maria?
[MARIA]
I-- Uh-- This is a bit much
for my poor virgin
eyes, that's all.
[LUCIFER] Hm. So that's how
the Demon Lord of Lust does it.
[ASMO moans]
[ASMO] You're so good.
You're all so good.
But I need much more of you!
I want to feel
you all inside me!
[ASMO moans]
Whatever! I can do that.
Great. This again.
That's some outfit
you've got there.
But in case you didn't notice,
this isn't a children's party.
[AUDIENCE]
Whoahhh!
[ASMO]
Is that a band-aid?
Don't make fun of
my panties, you creep!
Just watch--when Lucifer sees
my pole dance, she'll go nuts!
--[LEVI groans]
--[audience chatter]
[ASMO laughs]
It's harder than it looks, huh?
I-I'm just
getting warmed up!
[LUCIFER sighs]
This is just sad.
You won't win anyone's
hearts with those moves.
[audience chatter]
[ASMO] Like this!
You really have to feel it, see?
I'm feeling it fine,
thank you!
Good. Watch me closer.
Let your desires run free!
Just shut up!
I'm not listening to you!
[ASMO laughs]
[LEVI gasps]
What's happening?
I feel all hot
and tingly inside.
How is she doing this to me?
[ASMO] Don't be embarrassed.
Desire doesn't lie.
Listen to your body.
Let your lust be your guide.
[LEVI]
No! You're twisting my feelings!
Lucifer is the only one I want!
Please, just look at me.
Lucifer. I'm doing
this all for you!
Are you okay?
[MAN E]
That looked bad...
[ASMO laughs] I see
why Lucifer likes you.
[LUCIFER] Don't you dare
lay a finger on her.
Maria won't give in
to your power,
no matter how much you try.
She's far too pure.
Well, that is a real pity.
Time to go.
[MARIA]
Uh... Right.
[ASMO]
Hm.
[LEVI]
Ah! Lucifer!
[LUCIFER sighs]
That bitch really needs
to pull it together.
It looks like there's a
storm heading our way.
We never had anything
for dinner, did we?
I've never had a Cuban sandwich.
Why don't you go get one for me?
[MARIA]
Uh-- Right now?
Uh-huh. I'd hurry
if I were you.
[MARIA gasps]
[ASMO]
Why, hello!
[MARIA]
Oh. Uh, hello.
Lucifer's in the
hotel room right now.
I couldn't care
less about her.
You're the only one
I'm interested in.
[MARIA] Please, let me
go back. This is weird.
[ASMO] You've been
drawing me in ever since
I first laid eyes
on you at the beach.
Which I think is
rather unusual,
because you don't seem
interested in me one bit.
That goes for my
pole dancing as well.
I wonder what I could
be doing wrong...
I wouldn't take it
too personally.
[ASMO] Actually, I think
I know what it is.
You're a virgin, aren't you?
[MARIA gasps]
Wha... How did you...?
Uh... I mean, that...
That's none of your business.
And what does it matter?
Oh, my gosh, that's so cute.
It's actually pretty rare
these days, y'know.
Let's change the subject.
I'm, uh... uncomfortable.
[ASMO chuckles] Let me
help loosen you up a bit.
[MARIA] Could you loosen
these ties instead?
[ASMO] Everyone's scared
their first time,
but as you humans say, "Once
you pop, the fun don't stop."
--[ASMO] Ahh...
--[MARIA gasps]
[ASMO]
Well? Does that feel good?
Hmm?
[MARIA]
No way! I hate it!
[ASMO giggles]
Ahh! You are so cute!
I can't help it. I go crazy
when a girl gets shy!
There's only
one first time,
so you have to savor
every little moan.
[MARIA gasps]
[ASMO] That's good. You hold
out as long as you can.
We don't want this to be
over too soon, after all.
[MARIA shudders]
[ASMO gasps]
You're too perfect!
You keep fighting, but I can
feel your inhibitions crumbling.
And soon enough, you'll give in
to lust just like everyone else.
Slut.
[MARIA shudders]
[ASMO]
How about here?
[MARIA squeals]
Aha, that hit the spot.
[MARIA gasps]
No!
[MARIA pants]
[MARIA]
I can't take this.
Don't worry; I'll take
good care of you.
It's nothing to be ashamed of.
All humans are burdened with
the sin of lust, you know.
Fighting me is like
fighting your own nature.
It's time to submit.
That's not true.
[ASMO] You want to
feel good, don't you?
That's only natural.
[MARIA squeals, pants]
Tell me. What do
you want me to do?
Stop it!
Let me go. I've had enough.
It's too much.
Slow down. Be honest
with yourself.
Tell me what you really want.
[sound of glass breaking]
Playtime's over.
You're a bit late,
I'm afraid.
That pretty little toy of yours
belongs to me now.
Though I suppose you could stick
around and watch if you like.
Don't get ahead
of yourself.
[ASMO]
I see.
It would seem I can't snatch
her away so easily after all.
[LUCIFER] That's the idea.
I've taken a real liking to her.
In other words, if you really
want Maria that badly,
you'll have to
fight me for her.
[ASMO] Hm. I bet you
think you're so clever
for setting this up.
But I'll play your game,
because I am not letting
her go. Understand?
That's all you've got?
[LUCIFER grunts]
[LUCIFER gasps]
You like it? I thought
a little aromatherapy might
improve your mood. This is
the ultimate aphrodisiac.
[LUCIFER shudders]
[LUCIFER moans]
[ASMO] I like you much better
this way. Though to be frank,
I would have preferred an
uncorrupted angel to play with.
[LUCIFER squeals]
Wow, that is
quite the response.
All that squirming and moaning
from just a little foot massage?
[LUCIFER moans]
[ASMO] I must be
really good at my job!
How about I touch a more
sensitive spot next?
[LUCIFER]
What did you... do to me?
Like I said, this is
the ultimate aphrodisiac.
Its power has taken hold of
every inch of your body.
Watch this.
I'll make you scream.
[LUCIFER squeals]
We're finally having
some fun, aren't we?
Although I must admit,
I still prefer Maria.
There's nothing like
your first time.
On the other hand,
it's nice to break through
that tough exterior
of yours. I wonder...
What would make
you really lose it?
--[ASMO exhales]
--[LUCIFER squeals]
Hm. What kind of freak gets off
to a demon blowing
on their armpits?
Though actually,
there's no difference
between humans
and demons.
That is to say, deep down,
they're all freaks
who can only be saved
by my power of love.
That goes for Leviathan
as well, of course.
[LEVI moans]
[LUCIFER] You can't save shit
with your disgusting corruption.
Really?
[LUCIFER] That's right. All you
have to offer is base desire.
[LUCIFER gasps] Don't dress
it up with your flowery words
just so you can pretend
to be some goddess of love.
Lust is lust! Sex is sex!
And what's wrong
with that, may I ask?
[LUCIFER squeals]
[LUCIFER]
Not a damned thing.
If you ask me, there's
no sin in sex at all.
It's almost cute that
you think there is.
What? But I...
[LUCIFER gasps, pants]
You can get off to whatever
weird shit you want!
And people can have
all the sex they want--
that's their business!
[LUCIFER gasps]
Teach it! Preach it!
That's no sin at all!
What's happening?
My power... It's useless.
I have her right where I want
her, but I feel so defeated.
Why is she so beautiful?
Seeing her like this makes me
so ashamed of myself.
I don't want to watch.
But I can't look away.
[LUCIFER moans]
[ASMO gasps] Even for
the Demon Lord of Lust,
this is one hell of a turn-on!
[ASMO gasps] Why is this
turning me on so much?
Why is she so perfect?
I can't-- I can't
hold it back any longer!
Aahh! So good...!
Heh. Do your worst,
but my pride won't allow me
to admit defeat so easily.
[BELIAL] Huh? It seems one
of the Seven Commandments
was dispelled. That means
Asmodeus has fallen.
You want to challenge me,
Lucifer? Very well.
[ASMO] I underestimated
your worth.
If you wish to take my throne,
then please, do as you like.
[LUCIFER] I don't need it.
And to be perfectly honest,
I don't even want it.
But I do have a favor
to ask. Tell Belial
that her Commandments
are powerless before me.
Hm. Sure thing.
I did lose, after all.
So I won't stand
in your way anymore.
But you've got a long
road ahead of you.
[LUCIFER] Looks like
everything is back to normal.
Asmodeus' magic
has been dispelled.
[MARIA] She made the Demon Lord
of Lust lust after her.
That's kind of wrong, but at
least she saved everyone.
What's up? Are you mad
that I used you
as bait to lure Asmodeus?
[MARIA gasps] Wait, you're
telling me you used me as bait?
[LEVI]
Lucifer!
[LEVI giggles]
Let me put some suntan
lotion on your back!
Don't you dare. You're
just gonna screw it up.
[MARIA] I don't know
what to think anymore.
Is it wrong to believe in her?
To believe in a demon?
[LUCIFER] Shut up!
Shut up! I don't care!