[LUCIFER grunts]
We really have to
go down this cliff?
[sighs]This is going to
be a massive pain the ass!
[LUCIFER] Hm? Huh? So this
is what happens to people
when they kick the bucket.
Well, at least they're
having a good time.
[LUCIFER grunts]
[LUCIFER]
Uh?
[LUCIFER] We've just entered
the Second Circle of Hell.
I see why they call it the
Hell of Violent Storms.
[ASMO]
Well, well, well.
I didn't expect you to
come to me like this.
[BELIAL]
Where are the other Sins?
[ASMO] Oh, they decided to
return to their own hells.
So they can be there to welcome
Lucifer with open arms.
[BELIAL]
I see.
So the 7 mortal sins are
siding with a fallen angel?
What's next, all of
Hell will freeze over?
I think it's high time you
came clean about a few
important topics. Mainly,
I wanna know about Heaven.
I'm sure I have no idea
what you're talking about.
Vanity suits you,
"playing the fool" does not.
What makes you think
I'm playing the fool?
Your pheromones reek of
the scent of your lies.
I smell duplicity
and double-dealing
all over you, Belial!
[BELIAL gasps]
What are you doing?
[ASMO] You will tell me
why you betrayed Hell
or suffer the consequences
of your silence!
[BELIAL gasps]
[ASMO] You know I take an
incredible amount of pleasure
in watching you suffer.
I almost hope you
hold your tongue.
My mouth's watering at the
thought of torturing you.
[BELIAL] I see. You're going
to turn against me?
The leader of the 7 mortal sins?
[ASMO]
Leader?
Well, you've certainly
been leading the effort
to beguile us from
the very beginning.
Haven't you, Vanity?
[BELIAL]
Hmph!
[ASMO]
So you wanna be in charge?
[BELIAL]
Yes.
I'm going to amass enough
power to rival Heaven
and bring them to their knees.
I think you need a hobby.
The current state of the Sins
leaves us without
a proper leader.
We're weak and we're vulnerable.
We cannot defeat
Heaven like this.
That is why I'm paying
a visit to everyone
and imploring them
to hear me out.
I see. You're trying to
make an offensive move
against the armies of Heaven?
Ha! Count me in.
You want to organize the
ranks of Hell, do you?
We could use a little
development, I think.
Is there meat? If so, then yes.
[BELPHE]
That sounds like a real pain,
but if you wanna be the one
to do all of the hard work,
then knock yourself out.
[gasps]
You don't need my permission.
I'll support you,
no matter what.
You know that, don't you?
So what do you say?
Asmodeus, dark sin of lust?
Please let me be the leader.
Oh. Fine. Yes.
I don't know about you, but I
can't wait to get a real taste
of the Heavenly Host.
I'm getting all wet just
thinking about it.
Thank you very much.
[BELIAL chuckles]
[BELIAL chuckles] That certainly
brings memories to mind,
but let's get back to
the business at hand.
[gasps]
As leader of the seven sins, and
as a penance for your actions,
I command that Asmodeus,
Lord of Lust,
be punished for High Treason!
[ASMO shouts]
[ASMO gasps]
You can't do this, Belial!
You selected me to be the
leader of the sins, right?
As long as that decision stands,
none of you can
defy my authority!
[ASMO shouts]
[BELIAL] You'll regenerate just
a bit more quickly than my winds
can cut your skin and
tear into your flesh!
You of all people should
know pain is pleasure.
Perverts love that sort of
thing.
The pain feels too good! Oh! Oh!
[BELIAL chuckles]
[LUCIFER grunts]
This is wind is crazy strong.
[LUCIFER]
Who is that?
Oh damn. It's Asmodeus.
[ASMO gasps]
Lucifer. She got me good.
She brought me to
ecstasy many times over.
[LUCIFER]
Don't worry, I'll save you!
No, don't! I am the demon
lord of lust, remember?
All the pleasures of the flesh
fall under my dominion.
This will not defeat me.
I decided to choose you.
And I can live with that.
[shouts] You must hurry, Lucy.
Time is running out.
The rest of the sins
are in grave danger!
[ASMO grunts]
Belial is-- ow!
H-Hurry up and go.
Forget about me!
[ASMO screams]
This is so gross!
These are my good shoes too.
[LUCIFER grunts]
You're annoying. Spit it out.
Come on.
[LUCIFER gasps]
[BEELZE whimpers]
[LUCIFER]
Bub!
[BEELZE whimpers, coughs]
Let her go right now!
[BEELZE]
Lucifer. Don't...
But Bub?
It's okay. This is my atonement.
[LUCIFER gasps]
[BELIAL] So tell me:
how did Lucifer seduce you?
She gave me a lotta fun.
[BELIAL] She gave you "fun"?
Heh. You mean she gave you food.
Fine then. She's not the only
one who can feed your passion.
[BELIAL] Help me, and you
can help yourself, Bub.
No, thank you. I'm fine.
Just fine. Thanks.
I see.
[BEELZE whimpers]
When I tell you to eat, Missy.
You open up wide. Ha, ha, ha!
We cannot defy Belial.
I had no choice, Lucifer.
You must believe me.
Your meat is the only meat I
want to scarf down. I'm sorry.
[LUCIFER sighs] You're a
good little demon, Bub.
[chuckles]
[LUCIFER shouts]
No!
Bub!
[BEELZE] I must pay
my penance, Lucifer.
[LUCIFER] In order to
end your eternal Hell,
the leader of the Sins
will have to change!
[BEELZE whimpers]
Don't you worry about
a thing, all right?
This will all be over soon.
The meat you love'll
be yours again!
[MAMMON] So you've shown
your true colors at last.
What's wrong? Are you
regretting your choice?
Is the Lord of Greed
having buyer's remorse?
[MAMMON]
Don't be ridiculous.
All investments come with
a certain amount of risk.
But, the old adage is true:
the greater the risk,
the greater the
potential for reward.
[BELIAL]
How very greedy of you.
Am I to assume you've chosen
that fallen angel as your
next investment opportunity?
[MAMMON]
Yes. Lucifer's quite a woman,
her upside is too
big to pass up.
In fact, the opportunity
is so great,
I'm thinking about going all in.
Know what a gambler does when
the cards are bad? He folds.
You overplayed your hand!
[MAMMON gasps]
[MAMMON screams]
[BELIAL]
How unfortunate, Greed.
You bet all your money
on a losing horse
and now it's time to pay up.
[MAMMON grunts]
You're terrible!
Why would you betray
Hell like this, Belial?
Tell me: Has your vanity made
you forget you're a Byrnedale?
[BELIAL chuckles]
[GNOSIS] I'd like to ask
you something, if I may?
[BELIAL]
Anything.
[GNOSIS] You called
yourself Belial, did you not?
Why would you want to
inherit the Byrndale family?
[BELIAL]
You desire to know?
[GNOSIS]
Yes, I do indeed.
The Byrndales, a famous
family from Hell
known even in the farthest
reaches of Heaven.
Or should I say a
once famous family.
Your lineage is not what
it was, it's fallen, a mere
fragment of its former prestige
and illustrious eminence.
You're insane for trying
to inherit that disaster.
Are you bored out of your mind,
or are you trying to have
a little fun perhaps?
If you're just doing this on a
whim or trying to make yourself
look better, I will not
allow this to happen!
[BELIAL] If I told you I like
this dilapidated castle,
would that answer be
acceptable to you?
It has lost everything,
that's true.
Though it cannot
forget its former glory.
It is holding on to its vanity.
But it's not so much of
a fool to believe it can ever
return to its past.
I adore it, and I know it's
the best place for me now.
[GNOSIS] Tell me. Who are you?
You're not of Hell.
Could you be...?
I am the revered
Demon Lord of Vanity!
[GNOSIS]
Vanity?
[BELIAL] I promise you that I
will become the leader of the
Seven Mortal Sins, and in
so doing, I will make the
name Byrnedale known
throughout Hell once again!
And not only Hell! Beyond the
gates of Heaven, too!
[GNOSIS]
Hmph! A wishful lie.
[BELIAL]
I'll reclaim our former majesty.
Come on this journey
of reclamation,
and you have my word:
I will make this lie true!
It was the Byrnedale
family name alone
that gave you all the confidence
to trust in my leadership.
I'm quite certain if
some Demon Lord of
unknown lineage said
they wanted to become
leader of the Sins, no one would
pay them any heed at all.
Well It seems that
you've fooled me.
[BELIAL chuckles]
But, Belial.
[BELIAL]
Huh?
[MAMMON] Since I need
to recover my losses,
I'm in the market for a new
wager if you're interested.
Oh. So, shall we bet?
--[crashing]
--[MAMMON screams]
[BELIAL] Here's what I'd
like to wager, Mammon.
Before this is done, you'll
realize you're going to lose
everything you have if you
put your money on Lucifer!
[MAMMON] You don't
understand how it works.
Prosperity gathers where there's
confidence, not seeds of doubt.
You can't leave your money with
someone you have no trust in.
Not your money. Not your future!
[BELIAL] Are you saying you
trust Lucifer more than me?
Yes, that's what I'm
saying you wicked bitch!
--[crashing]
--[screams]
[BELIAL]
As you know, Greed,
every mistake comes
with a price.
I hope you enjoy paying
for yours. Ha, ha, ha.
[MAMMON screams]
[LUCIFER]
What are you doing now?
That Levi, damn her. So this
is the Fifth Circle of Hell.
[ASTA grunts]
Give up, Asta you're
gonna lose!
I've made my choice! I'm going
to fight on Lucifer's Side!
♪ I'm Belial's sheild bitch,
it's what I'm meant to do. ♪
♪ Since she was good to me,
then I 'moan be bad to you. ♪
[LEVI] No matter how angry
or annoyed Lucifer is with me,
she always comes home
to me, she loves me!
Nothing you say'll make
me change my mind!
[ASTA] ♪ You know she's
using you but you're to ♪
♪blind to see the truth,
but my ryhmes are here♪
♪and clear so let me
offer you some proof.♪
♪ Lucifer don't love you, can
you pick up what I'm spittin? ♪
♪She loves that human girl,
you know it, she is smitten.♪
[LEVI]
Shut up!
[ASTA grunts]
Yuk. This is so disgusting.
[yelps]
[LEVI laughs]
Serves you right!
[ASTRA grunts]
[laughs, grunts]
I got you back!
[LEVI growls] I'm gonna
make you regret that!
[ASTA gasps]
[LEVI]
Suck on this!
[ASTA]
Stop it!
[BELPHE gasps, groans]
[BELPHE whimpers]
I can't take this anymore!
I really hate not
being able to breathe!
[BELPHE gasps] I don't wanna
do this anymore! I'm sorry!
[BELPHE yelps]
Please! Trade with me! I'll be
your best friend forever!
Uh, no. Besides, in my opinion,
you need some excersize fatty.
Good luck with the cardio.
Huh?! Wait, you can't leave
me here like this! Ah!
Please make it stop! Oh, no!
[LUCIFER] So this is where
violent souls go to rest?
[LUCIFER] I don't have
the time or the patience
to deal with you!
[LUCIFER] The Eighth
Circle is just below.
Mm. I can't get down there!
[LUCIFER gasps]
[SIREN A groans]
[LUCIFER]
Perfect.
[LUCIFER grunts]
Eighth Circle? Here we come!
[SATAN]
Lord Belial,
did you know that Heaven was
going to attack Hell? Answer me!
[BELIAL]
Yes. Obviously.
I don't appreciate your tone!
Am I to infer from this
that you have connections
beyond the gates?
Maybe I do, maybe I don't.
What's it to you?
So Lord Lucifer was right
all along! Damn you.
You're nothing but a
double-dealing fraud!
You said when the day came that
you were going to attack heaven
with all the rest of us,
but I'm assuming that was a
lie too, you deceitful whore!
I've had enough
of your treachery!
[BELIAL] At the time,
it's what I thought.
I believed it was the only
viable option we had.
At the time? What are
you trying to say?
I'm saying that the
situation has changed.
The only thing that's left is to
wait until the hour is upon us,
and brace for impact!
[SATAN grunts]
Satan. You will accept your
penance for the crime of
defying my authority.
[SATAN gasps]
[BELIAL]
Don't worry.
The dissolved departed
cover up everything here.
Wait, you're the dead
scum from the other day.
Have you fallen this far?
[shouts]
[BELIAL]
Oh, I forgot.
All of the fallen dead,
even in their degeneracy,
thirst for the smooth, silky
confection of a woman's body.
You look like you're
enjoying yourself.
[LUCIFER]
Belial!
[BELIAL]
You're late to the party.
Sadly for you, there's no one
left to take your side, Lucifer!
[BELIAL laughs]
Always quick to
run away, that one.
You must be very careful.
[LUCIFER grunts]
Please, she is mighty.
Her power grows
stronger by the minute.
I fear she is more
powerful than all of us.
Yes, I know.
[LEVI]
Whale. Do it!
[WHALE A roars]
[ASTA] Hey! You can't
use servants! That's cheating!
[LEVI shouts] You're not
supposed to topple over, Whale!
[ASTA] Well, that was
certainly anti-climactic!
If we don't do something quick
we're gonna be gonners! Help!
[ASTA] I don't have
any magic left.
I suppose I could do
another rap ballad?
[LEVI] I don't want a song!
I want you to save our asses!
[ASTA]
Too late.
[BELIAL]
Wake up.
[MARIA gasps]
[BELIAL] I need your help and
you're going to give it to me.
In so doing, we will bring a new
fearsome power to my Dáinsleif.
[MARIA gasps]
Stop it.
[BELIAL chuckles]
[MARIA gasps]
[BELIAL]
Angel blood. I knew it.
She's as cunning
as she is shrewd.
What better place to hide
Angel's Blood than in the veins
of a human.
[gasps]
I don't understand.
[BELIAL] This is all about
Lucifer having her
chance to return to Heaven.
[MARIA gasps]
[LUCIFER] I'll entrust
an angel's life to you.
[gasps]
What's wrong? Did you not
realize you were being used
till just this moment?
Don't worry.
A plan can come to an end
just as quickly as it starts.
[MARIA screams]
[LUCIFER]
The Ninth Circle. Cocytus.
The giants, sealed in this
eternal frozen ice Hell,
are from the
ancient age of myth.
Those that rebelled against God
and were defeated
by the Holy Armies.
[gasps]
[LUCIFER grunts]
[GIANT A roars]
[LUCIFER shouts]
[LUCIFER]
Belial, you crafty bitch.
So, this is the last barrier
I have to break through?
[LUCIFER grunts]
[LUCIFER] If you really
think these oversized freaks
could hold me back, then you
don't know me at all!
[GIANT A groans]
You're gonna hafta do
better than that!
[LUCIFER grunts]
They're tougher than I thought.
Look! In case you
hadn't noticed,
I'm a little busy right now!
[LEVI]
Lucifer!
[LUCIFER]
Huh?
Levi what the hell?
[LEVI]
Save me!
[LUCIFER] Sorry, you're on
your own! Good luck!
[LUCIFER pants]
You're trying to force
me to use the last bit
of my magic on
these sorry ass giants.
You guys tried to defeat
Heaven and lost everything.
Guess what?
I'm gonna try, too!
But I'm gonna win!
[LUCIFER pants]
[LUCIFER]
Hm! I actually made it.
[exhales]
Maria. I'm coming for you.
[laughs]