[ASTA] ♪ That's right--
livin' like a demon ♪
♪ got me breakin'
all the rules! ♪
♪ Get out of my face
with anything that's cute! ♪
♪ You know, most of this place
is a huge freakin' tragedy ♪
♪ I'll tear apart all these
dolls with my melody ♪
♪ That's the reason I
came in the first place ♪
♪ My heart was on fire
and I needed a change ♪
♪ But it was so stupid, stupid,
I shouldn't even be here ♪
♪ Screw everything, it makes me
wanna scream, "God damn!" ♪
[ASTA]
♪ That's right... ♪
[MARIA] I think she recorded
it in a karaoke booth
then uploaded it as soon
as she was done.
It's got a whole ton
of views already!
Lots of comments, too.
♪ I'll tear apart all these
dolls with my melody... ♪
[LUCIFER] Hm. She's not bad.
I'm surprised.
Lyrics are kind of
a downer, though.
[MARIA] She is the
Demon Lord of Melancholy.
[LEVI] Uh-- She came out!
Let's follow her!
[ASTA sighs]
[LUCIFER] Wait, you're
telling me she only has
internet followers?
A human could do that.
And what's the point?
You can't even enslave them!
I thought she was supposed
to be a Demon Lord.
[MARIA] Sounds like
a relief to me.
Pricy, but worth it.
This is too cute.
[ASTA gasps]
[ASTA shudders]
♪ Whatchoo think you're doin'
bustin' into my place? ♪
♪ Betta wipe that grin
off your face! ♪
Astaroth, correct?
And melancholy is your sin,
I believe? Your shit is
about to get wrecked.
♪ I dunno if you're crazy
or you're really just bored, ♪
♪ but you shouldn't pick a
fight with a Demon Lord! ♪
[LUCIFER] Cute, but you
can't intimidate me.
[ASTA gasps]
Look, bitch.
Lucifer is taking down
the Seven Mortal Sins
one by one
and you're the next
name on her hit list.
I know you're scared!
Don't pee yourself!
♪ Y'all don't know me!
Come on, get real! ♪
♪ I ain't scared of nobody--
don't tell me how I feel! ♪
[LUCIFER] Can we stop rapping
and start fighting already?
You're wasting my time.
[ASTA]
I did pee... a little.
♪ I'm a rapper,
not a fighter-- ♪
♪ don't you know
how this works? ♪
♪ Get out of my face--
get gone, you fat jerk! ♪
[LUCIFER] ♪ I'll tear apart all
these dolls with my melody ♪
♪ That's the reason I
came in the first place ♪
♪ My heart was on fire
and I needed a change ♪
♪ But it was so stupid, stupid,
I shouldn't even be here ♪
♪ Screw everything, it makes me
wanna scream, "God damn!" ♪
[LUCIFER] I'm more into
crushing things with my fists
than "crushing it"
in the studio.
Are you sure a music battle
is the way to go?
That was amazing! You nailed it!
You'll knock her dead!
[LUCIFER]
If you say so.
I just posted it online.
I need something to eat,
and maybe a drink or two.
Let's go someplace fancy!
[LEVI]
Fatty tuna!
Saké!
I never knew you had such
a beautiful singing voice.
I guess I shouldn't
be surprised.
You are an angel, after all.
Don't ever say that again.
You'll ruin the food.
We need two orders
of sea urchin, 'kay?
None for you, Maria.
You suck!
[phone chimes]
[MARIA] Uh, I should see how
our video channel's doing.
It's hardly been up an hour,
but we've already got
twenty thousand views
and lots of favorites, too!
Oh, yeah?
'Cause Lucifer's
awesome, obviously!
Why does this
still surprise you?
I swear, I'm the only one
who appreciates her!
[ASTA] ♪ She's really
throwing down. ♪
♪ I didn't think that
she could sing. ♪
♪ It happened so fast--
she can do anything. ♪
♪ She's gettin' so many hits,
she aint gonna submit-- ♪
♪ this fallen angel lady
makes me feel like shit. ♪
Mm! She's back for more?
It's been a while...
Miss Melancholy.
So long in fact,
that your seat in Hell
has grown cold
in your absence.
[ASTA gasps]
Uh-- Hey, Belial.
[BELIAL] You seem
terribly ill at ease.
It's... Lucifer. She...
[BELIAL] You saw her?
She was here?
She truly is determined
to harass us.
What a loathsome little
heavenspawn she is!
It appears that I'll have to
take matters into my own hands.
Don't back down. I'll help you.
With me at your side,
she's done for.
You have no need to worry.
[ASTA sighs]
[ASTA]
I'm supposed to beat her?
But how?
[phone chimes]
[BELPHE] You see Lucifer's
video, Asta?
[ASTA]
Uh-huh.
[BELPHE] Why'd she do a cover
of your song? What happened?
[ASTA] Yesterday she
and her friends busted into
my apartment. She said she
was gonna "wreck my shit."
[BELPHE] She's putting
the smack down.
[ASTA]
Yep.
[BELPHE]
What's wrong? You worried?
[ASTA] There's no way
I can compete with her.
She shines as bright as the sun.
[BELPHE] I dunno. When you sing,
you're pretty shiny yourself.
[ASTA]
Shiny?
[BELPHE]
But dark, too.
[ASTA] Wait. So am I
shiny or am I dark?
[BELPHE] You're a darkness
that swallows up the light!
[ASTA] She'll swallow
me up instead.
There won't be anything left.
[BELPHE]
Nuh-uh. No way.
[ASTA] I wish I could just die
now and get it over with.
[BELPHE] Asta, come home.
I miss you.
Asta? You there?
[LEVI]
Cool! We got their attention.
We're gonna steal all her
fans with the next one!
All right, but let's make
an original song this time.
And nothing sappy or depressing.
That's so not my style.
[MARIA] So, uh, what
were you thinking?
Oh! I get it! You don't
wanna sing a demon-y song--
you wanna sing a song
that's pretty and stuff
because you're an angel!
[LUCIFER] For the last time,
I'm not an angel anymore.
Now think. There's got
to be something evil
that's also catchy
and upbeat, right?
Well, I guess pop
music is pretty evil
and it's definitely catchy.
[LEVI]
Are you stupid?
She can't sell out yet!
It's her first single!
If you've got a plan,
Maria, let's hear it.
[MARIA]
Uh...? Mm...
You could be a teen idol...
[LEVI] That doesn't work
at all! Lucifer is cool
and sophisticated!
She's not some
manufactured teeny-bopper
no-talent schoolgirl!
Levi. Cool it.
Maybe she's right. You couldn't
pull that off. No way.
[LUCIFER]
What?
There's not a damn thing
I can't pull off.
An idol? Are you kidding me?
Bring it on. That's too easy!
And here's a secret.
When I was in Heaven...
I listened to idol
singers all the time!
That is so cute! Maybe a
little sad, but mostly cute!
I can't wait to see
this new side of you!
[LEVI] Okay, let's get
to work! And action!
[LUCIFER] ♪ That's right--
livin' like a demon ♪
♪ got me breakin'
all the rules! ♪
♪ Get out of my face
with anything that's cute! ♪
♪ You know, most of this place
is a huge freakin' tragedy ♪
♪ I'll tear apart all these
dolls with my melody ♪
♪ That's the reason I
came in the first place ♪
♪ My heart was on fire
and I needed a change ♪
♪ But it was so stupid, stupid,
I shouldn't even be here ♪
♪ Screw everything, it makes me
wanna scream, "God damn!" ♪
[MARIA gasps]
It's a huge hit already!
I was wrong.
You nailed it!
[LEVI] Of course she did!
Lucifer's perfect at everything!
[MARIA] Mm. Looks like
Astaroth made a new video too.
Should we watch?
[ASTA] ♪ I creep
from the shadows ♪
♪ and I swallow up the light ♪
♪ Put some sorrow in your soul
and I win without a fight... ♪
[LUCIFER] What is this?
It sucks.
[MARIA] I don't get it either.
But it's beating us in views.
We're gonna lose to this garbage
and it's all your fault!
Don't you have anything to say?
How're you gonna fix this?
[LEVI, MARIA gasp]
Lucifer, wait.
You shouldn't feel bad.
You were great! I just...
[LUCIFER] Am I really going
to lose to that sorry excuse
for a Demon Lord?
[LUCIFER sighs]
[MICHAEL]
Curb your pride, Lucifer.
Even if you're the leader
of the Seven Virtues,
I won't allow you to
blaspheme the word of God.
[LUCIFER] If God is wrong,
I'm going to correct them!
I'm the only one qualified to!
[MICHAEL] That is
the pride I speak of.
I'm sorry, but I'm
in the right here!
[MICHAEL] I had hoped
it wouldn't come to this.
Michael. Stop kidding yourself.
You can't defeat me.
Deaf to the words of God,
you are no longer an angel.
Now, you shall fall, Lucifer!
[LUCIFER] I won't lose again!
I'm stronger than that!
[ASTA] ♪ That's right--
livin' like a demon ♪
♪ got me breakin'
all the rules! ♪
♪ Get out of my face
with anything that's cute! ♪
♪ You know, most of this place
is a huge freakin' tragedy ♪
♪ I'll tear apart all these
dolls with my melody ♪
♪ That's the reason I
came in the first place ♪
♪ My heart was on fire
and I needed a change ♪
♪ But it was so stupid, stupid,
I shouldn't even be here ♪
♪ Screw everything, it makes me
wanna scream, "God damn!" ♪
[LUCIFER] ♪ All of her rhymes
are drilling in my head. ♪
♪ My heart is falling apart
and I'm wishing I was dead. ♪
♪ If I jump, maybe I'll be
free from this dread? ♪
♪ Or maybe just fall
and I'll die instead? ♪
Melancholy, huh?
Sorry, I'll pass.
I won't lose to
something like that.
[BELIAL]
Is that so?
[LUCIFER gasps]
And what makes you think
the battle is over?
Belial? I'm surprised you
dragged your fat ass
all the way here. If you
want to beg for mercy,
it's far too late.
I'll ignore that. There's
something I wanted to ask you.
Otherwise, I would have kept
my posterior back in Hell.
What?
I'll be blunt, so we
can get this over with.
When you fell from Heaven,
what was your goal?
[LUCIFER chuckles] You really
think I'm going to answer that?
Come on.
As impertinent as ever,
I see. But you'll tell me
soon enough, when Astaroth
brings you to your knees.
[LUCIFER] You're always
good for a laugh, Belial.
And it's going to be a riot
when I defeat you and Astaroth.
I don't know what to say.
It's you. I'm feeling merciful,
so I'll give you
one more chance.
You'd better come up with
a damn good plan this time.
Don't worry, I already have!
Leave it to me!
[LUCIFER]
♪ Give me a favor! ♪
♪ My heart is beating
so fast... Dancin'! ♪
♪ Don't want another day
to pass me by ♪
♪ Don't want to be alone ♪
♪ I want to make sure
that this feeling's right ♪
♪ I don't want to go home ♪
♪ Maybe it is fate that we're
perfect together as one ♪
♪ I'm sorry, I didn't mean
that at all, but it's done ♪
[LUCIFER] ♪ Could this be love,
or is it friendship? ♪
♪ I feel the start of
a slight fever dance ♪
♪ It's not enough--
I need more and more ♪
♪ My heart is beating
so fast... Dancin'! ♪
♪ I wanna be with you!
Hug me tight! ♪
♪ I'll wait for your love;
don't you leave me now! ♪
♪ Hold me forever!
Stay by my side! ♪
♪ I'm just a girl
that needs you ♪
♪ Will you forgive me
for feeling this way? ♪
Whoa. That's so cute,
and, like, sexy, too.
It's time for your major debut.
Frankly, Lucifer is tough.
If we want to defeat her, I'm
afraid we'll have to go big.
I guess...
[BELPHE] Don't even worry, Asta.
You can totally own her.
For real, girl.
♪ I know for a Demon Lord,
I'm really pretty weak, ♪
♪ but when it comes to droppin'
rhymes my skills are unique. ♪
♪ I mean, I'm ready
to throw down, ♪
♪ never wanna slow down, ♪
♪ gonna beat Lucifer
and take the crown. ♪
How bout dat, y'all?
[BELPHE] Hell, yeah!
That's more like it.
With my help, your shows
are guaranteed to sell out.
All that I ask...
...is that you destroy
Lucifer with your song.
I'll direct your music video
and make sure it's super fresh.
[BELIAL chuckles]
[ASTA]
♪ Rock you! ♪
[ASTA] ♪ Your blindness
cannot ever be saved! ♪
♪ Sinning the way that
you want without shame! ♪
♪ Bored and mediocre, following
whatever the flow desires ♪
♪ Will destroy the world! ♪
♪ Volatile stupidness,
fall into the great abyss ♪
♪ Humankind comes
when the rain begins ♪
♪ Idiotic people buy these
crazy made-up fantasies ♪
♪ They believe that
"to live is to dream"! ♪
♪ Wandering nomad,
I am without any purpose ♪
♪ Rotten platitudes feel hollow
underneath their surface ♪
♪ Pure love entangled,
intricate and truthful ♪
♪ Doesn't have a place
where it can go ♪
♪ I just wish that everybody
would simply disappear ♪
♪ Along with this whole world
that they hold dear! ♪
♪ (Say goodbye!)
If this reality ♪
♪ (Won't you die?)
Is doomed beyond saving ♪
♪ (Say goodbye!)
It's better that you live ♪
♪ Smiling mockingly at it ♪
♪ Languid melancholy is how I
deal and reveal my true face ♪
♪ A grave wind of death and
impending darkness blows ♪
♪ Raise your fists
and beware tomorrow ♪
I promised you a full house
and I always deliver.
[ASTA shudders]
I have TV interviews
lined up too.
[ASTA whimpers]
[BELPHE] You're pretty
popular now, Asta.
All that hard work is
finally paying off!
[cheers and applause]
[ASTA shudders]
Stop wasting
our time already.
Are you gonna start
this thing or what?
Maybe something
happened to her.
[LUCIFER] Astaroth?
She won't show.
[MARIA gasps]
Why not?
[LUCIFER] It's obvious.
Why do you think she recorded
all her songs alone
in a karaoke room?
Stage fright. She can't
play in front of a crowd.
[LUCIFER]
She's shutting down.
[music begins,
audience cheers]
[ASTA shudders]
[BELPHE]
Asta! What the hell?
Why are you
running off? Stop!
[GUY A] Is this
happening or not?
[GIRL B] Wish they'd
say something.
[GUY C]
It's gotta be a stunt.
[GIRL D]
Well, it's pissing me off.
[GUY E]
Seriously?
[GUY F] I could be at home
watching porn right now.
[GUY G] Maybe she's
not even real.
[GUY H] You think
she's, like, CG?
[GIRL I] Have some faith
in Astaroth, guys.
[GUY J] She's not exactly
earning it, is she?
[excited audience chatter]
I'm about to rock your world.
[LEVI] Woo! Bring the
house down, Lucifer!
You're so cool!
[ASTA] I can't do it.
I can't. I can't. I can't.
There's too many people.
They're all staring at me.
[BELIAL] Astaroth! Get your
melancholy ass out there
and sing! Lucifer took your
spot on the stage! Stop her!
[ASTA] I give up. Help me.
Let me go home. I hate this.
[BELPHE] Okay, cool,
that's perfectly fine!
Let's just you and me
go back to Hell, Asta.
I'd rather be napping, anyway.
[LUCIFER sings
in the background]
Don't say that!
[BELPHE] But if you do wanna
stay, I think the audience
really likes you. You don't
have to say anything.
Just tell 'em them how
you feel with your song.
With my song. Of course!
[LUCIFER] ♪ ...I didn't mean
that at all, but it's done ♪
[ASTA screams]
She's here at last! It's the
Languid Diva. Astaroth!
[ASTA] Sorry to keep
you waiting so long!
[audience cheers]
[ASTA]
Hm...?
Sure took your time. So are
we gonna have our music battle
or not? The stage is set if
you've got the guts for it.
Fair enough, Lucifer. We'll
fight, but I'mma warn you.
I'm taking this stage back,
no matter what!
♪ Say goodbye... ♪
♪ Could this be love,
or is it friendship? ♪
♪ I feel the start of
a slight fever dance ♪
♪ It's not enough--
I need more and more ♪
♪ My heart is
beating so fast... ♪
♪ Tomorrow! ♪
Rock you!
♪ Don't want another day
to pass me by ♪
♪ Don't want to be alone ♪
♪ I want to make sure
that this feeling's right ♪
♪ I don't want to go home ♪
♪ Your blindness cannot
ever be saved! ♪
♪ Sinning the way that
you want without shame! ♪
♪ Bored and mediocre, following
whatever the flow desires ♪
♪ Will destroy the world! ♪
♪ Volatile stupidness,
fall into the great abyss ♪
♪ Humankind comes
when the rain begins ♪
♪ Idiotic people buy these
crazy made-up fantasies ♪
♪ They believe that
"to live is to dream"! ♪
♪ Could this be love,
or is it friendship? ♪
♪ I feel the start of
a slight fever dance ♪
♪ It's not enough--
I need more and more ♪
♪ Smiling mockingly at it ♪
[LUCIFER]
♪ Dancin'! ♪
♪ I wanna be with you!
Hug me tight! ♪
♪ I'll wait for your love;
don't you leave me now! ♪
♪ Raise your fists
and beware tomorrow ♪
♪ My heart is
beating so fast... ♪
♪ Tomorrow! ♪
[audience cheers]
[BELIAL groans]
[ASTA]
You really kicked my ass.
Clearly, I was better, but you
still held your own out there.
I wouldn't feel too bad.
So, are you gonna stick
with your music career?
[ASTA] Yeah. I love
singing too much to quit.
As for the crowds...
I still need some work.
Maybe I'll start
with a street live.
I'm done with
the whole thing.
Why would you stop?
You're so talented!
[LUCIFER] Yeah, but I
don't wanna deal with
the autograph sessions
and fan club crap.
She'd make the fans
lick her boots, I bet.
Okay, we're out of here.
[ASTA]
One last thing.
[LUCIFER]
Mm?
[ASTA] The next time I see you,
we'll have to fight for reals.
Our duet was tight, but I'm
still with Belial. I'm sorry.
So that's how it is.
A loyal dog after all.
It's kind of cute.
[MARIA] I'm sorry about before.
I'm glad things worked out.
Maria?
[MARIA]
Yes?
Loosen up a bit.
We're friends now, aren't we?
[MARIA gasps]
[LEVI] Lucifer,
I brought you a drink!
[LUCIFER]
I'm not thirsty.
[LEVI] Aww! But I didn't
put my lips on it this time!
Not much at least!
We're friends.
[MARIA chuckles]