[PATRON 1A]
Another round.
[SERVER 1A]
Here ya go.
We got boobs and booze
at our club. Yeah!
[WOMAN 1A]
Come back soon, okay?
[PATRON 1B]
And, then he fell on his face!
[PATRONS laugh]
So, what? You my long-lost kid?
Decent guess, but no.
You're just a man
I was hired to kill.
[gasps]
[knocking]
Whatever you're selling,
we don't want it.
[LIN]
Takashi's here, right?
--[gasps]
--I need to talk to him.
Apparently, he's been
cheating on me.
He slept with you ?
Looks like you
misunderstood the--
[LIN] I'm not trying
to get back with him.
He got me this bag as a present.
And I would like to return it.
Preferably by beating him
upside the head with it.
Know what?
He could use a wake-up call.
Just make it quick, okay?
[gasps]
[TAKASHI]
Hey, Akemi. Is someone there?
[gasps]
I really do hate it when
I have to knock off women.
[TAKASHI gasps]
Who the hell are you?
Who, me? I'm just a hitman.
[gasps, yelps]
You goddamn coward!
You even dressed up to trick us?
[LIN]
Idiot.
I wear this outfit
'cause it looks good.
I mean, give me a break.
Do you think it's
easy to kill in heels?
Now tell me.
What do you know
about the organization
behind club Miroir?
Surely enough to know
what happens to people
who steal from them?
Look, they can have the money!
I still have 4,000,000!
That's less than half of it.
Regardless, they seem to be
over getting the money back.
They just wanna make
an example of you.
[TAKASHI]
Then you take the money!
I'll show you where
it is, if you--
If I let you walk away?
An interesting proposition.
I have some financial problems
of my own, so that's
not a bad offer.
[gasps]
[LIN]
Here's the thing.
Once I take a job,
I have to follow through.
After all, I am a professional.
[BANBA] Uh-huh. Another home
run. Looks like I still got it.
Damn she's hot!
I'm busy, or I'd kick your ass.
[phone vibrates]
[LIN]
Zhang again? What do you want?
If it's about the couple
that stole your money they--
Huh?! Another one? I only
just finished the last job.
Hold on. You mean this
one's a detective?
Hope I don't have to remind you
that bluebloods cost double.
Yeah, I know. Just send
me the address already.
[LIN] Soon I can forget
I knew this piece of shit.
Once I've paid off
the money I owe.
[LIN]
Qiaomei.
[QIAOMEI]
Brother! Brother!
Don't leave me! Please!
Just hang in there, sis.
I'll get you back. Soon.
[GWEN] Wait, don't you start
at the Fukuoka branch today?
Yeah.
I was on my way to
catch the bullet train
when I realized I'd left this.
What, did you win a big
game with that ball?
[SAITO] I'd rather not get
into it, but this definitely
isn't something I can forget.
We only worked together
for a couple months,
but you taught me a lot.
Thank you, Gwen.
Nah, man, you don't
owe me anything.
Best of luck, Saito,
and good hunting.
Thanks, I think I'll need it.
I hear three percent
of Fukuoka's population
is in our line of work.
Hope a wimp like me can compete.
[SARUWATARI]
That's it?!
What's a guy gotta do to get
a real job around here?
C'mon you know I'm
the best cleaner
you got in this place.
Gimme a friggin' challenge man!
I think he's better suited
for this kind of career.
Yeah, he's in a
league of his own.
Well, keep in touch.
[GWEN]
Sounds good.
[SAITO yelps]
[SAITO sighs]
[GWEN] This line of work
really doesn't suit you.
Working at a company
of killers for hire?
Gotta wonder what
made you join us.
[LIN]
This is the place, but...
[WOMAN 1B]
They say he hung himself.
I heard his wife just left him.
Wonder if that's
what drove him to it.
Or it could've been job stress.
I think Takeda was a detective.
[gasps]
He killed himself?
Well, if he did the
job for me, so be it.
If I see him in hell,
I'll have to thank him.
Yeah, it's me. Your
detective is no more.
[BANBA] There're two small
bruises beneath the rope mark.
They were clearly
left by fingers.
Whoever ruled this a suicide
must've been drunk.
Yeah, I had the same thought.
Careful. Looks like
the work of a pro.
Who's the victim?
Well, his name was Takeda,
and he was the
detective in charge
of the gang unit in my precinct.
Good man. They found
his body this morning.
According to the note,
he offed himself
because he was about to be
found out for stealing evidence.
I see. What do you
think happened?
That's the question.
He looked out for me
when I was younger.
Sometimes you try to throw
a rising fastball, and it dips.
And for Takeda,
that happened quite a bit.
[SHIGEMATSU] This was slipped
under my door yesterday.
No return address, but I
know it was from him.
The night before he
was killed, huh?
I guess he must've suspected.
What the--? That man...
Yeah.
[HARADA]
In the last four years,
we've made the Hakata ward both
safer and more prosperous.
But there's still
work to be done.
In the next four years, I assure
you that, if re-elected,
I'll work tirelessly to
make our city even greater.
[BANBA]
It's the mayor himself.
He's got the same
babe with him, too.
[HARADA] And so, I ask each
of you to lend me your support
in the upcoming
mayoral election!
[applause]
[pop]
What was that about?
I was curious about how
the broad would react,
that's all.
So you meant it
to sound like a gun.
[BANBA]
A secretary would've frozen up.
A bodyguard would've
moved to shield him.
[SHIGEMATSU]
But she did neither.
[BANBA]
That was a hitman's reaction.
That said, I don't think she's
the one who took out Takeda.
Nails that long
would break skin.
Heh. You've got
some sharp eyes.
So listen, Banba.
That favor I wanted to a--
No problem.
Wha--?
Whatever it is that
Mayor Harada's getting up to,
we know he's at
least corrupt enough
to have hired
himself an assassin.
Bastard's got dirty laundry.
Let's air it out.
You have a good day
at the office, Reiko?
Have anything to report?
Thought someone fired a gun.
But as it turned out,
it was a false alarm.
Just some idiot
popping a balloon.
What about your end?
Ivanov tells me he got it done.
The detective's death
will be deemed a suicide.
And thanks to yours
truly, he'll soon be
just some dirty cop
who stole evidence.
[sighs] Do you really think
all of this was necessary?
[SHINO]
Who knows?
It doesn't matter.
We're public servants now.
Which means we do as
we're told by our betters.
[phone vibrates]
Speak of the friggin' devil.
--Hello, sir--
--[YUSUKE] Munakata, hey!
It's me again.
[REIKO]
That little creep.
Sorry, bud. I made
another oopsie.
You can come clean
it up for me, right?
Ah, thanks a million.
Nah, take your time.
No rush at all.
Ah, you're the best.
[SAITO]
So this is the city where
three in 100 people are hitmen.
[SAITO]
Hakata...
Come on, Saito! Get it together!
[SAITO]
Now, where's the bus stop.
[ENOKIDA]
You've always had a penchant
for sticking your neck out.
But this is serious.
[BANBA]
Yeah.
This has already cost
one person their life.
[ENOKIDA]
Wow, ya don't say.
Sounds exciting.
[BANBA] Anyway, how's
it lookin', Enokida?
Can ya do it?
Come on, Banba. That question
barely merits a response.
I could turn every traffic
light in this city red
if I felt like it.
Want me to do that now?
I've already hacked these guys.
Oh. Wow.
Here's the file on your girl.
Asakura Reiko.
Used to work at Red Rum Inc.,
but quit five years ago.
Well, I guess
that confirms it.
Yup. We all know what
that company does.
They might as well
go by Murder Inc.
It's a company of assassins,
plain and simple.
So, yeah. Just as you
suspected. She's a cleaner.
Reiko's a former club hostess.
And her specialty is poisons.
A face like that is just lethal.
I bet she poisons
her victims slowly.
Spikes their drinks between
kisses and cuddles.
Scary.
That's all the info
there is on her.
Guess we can assume she spent
the past five years
working for the mayor.
It's possible that
he sought her out.
Seems useful, having a lady
hitman pose as your secretary.
What about other employees?
Is there anyone else who
quit around that time?
Someone who likes
to kill by strangling?
Strangling?
Yeah. Think I did see a guy.
Ivanov Hisashi. Half
Japanese, half Russian.
Kills both through ligature
and manual strangulation.
So. This girl. Who is she?
[YUSUKE] She's nobody. Just
some girl off the streets.
She started makin' a fuss
about lettin' me bang her,
so I lost my temper.
Who's this kid think he is?
Ivanov.
Okay, you take that end, Shino.
[SHINO] Manual labor wasn't
part of my job description.
[elevator dings]
[REIKO] I'm not sure if they
covered this in private school,
but murder is illegal.
Heh, I get it, that's
a really good one.
'Cause you're an assassin.
I like ironic humor.
[YUSUKE] Look, Reiko, it's not
like I wanna cause you trouble.
But you know. I'm a growin' boy.
I get urges.
Listen, you brat...
Aw, don't get mad at me.
I gave proper notice
this time, didn't I?
[REIKO]
That's not the point.
We can't be carting bodies
out of here every other week.
How much effort do you think
it takes to cover up--
My apologies.
This causes your father a
great deal of trouble as well.
Do you get that?
And you think I care about that?
Why the hell should I?
Bye! Thanks for
your future service!
[FOREIGNER 1A]
Stop! Please! Don't do this!
[THUGS, FOREINGER 1A shouting]
What is that?
Oh, this?
My friends started
a King's Game club,
and I decreed that they
beat up some foreigners.
And filmed it, of course.
Isn't it fun?
Y'know, I was thinking
I might post it online.
Huh?
You won't be uploading anything.
Furthermore, I want
the name of every
friend of yours who was there.
I'm not letting this get out.
Yeah, Munakata?
We have a new crisis
on our hands.
[FOREIGNER 1A]
My friend and I were just
walking through a park.
And three guys attacked
us out of nowhere!
I thought they'd kill me.
So I ran away, but my friend...
It's okay. Don't force
yourself to talk.
The man's friend is in
the hospital right now,
comatose, and in
critical condition.
Bastards lynched him.
[FOREIGNER 1A]
When I saw him in the hospital,
he had this in his hand.
I think it belonged
to one of them.
[JIRO]
Murase Jun? All right, then.
What exactly are you after?
I want revenge!
Then your avenger will
be dispatched shortly,
[FOREIGNER 1A sobs]
[SAITO] Murase Jun. The
target's a college student?
Yeah, the client's an
older neighbor of his.
Says the kid's a nuisance,
always causin' a racket.
Can ya shut him up for good?
Uh! Yes!
Look at you.
Bright eyed and bushy tailed.
Oh! Let's see here.
Got some business cards for ya.
From this day forward,
you're Ito Takuya.
[SAITO] Thank you very much,
sir. I'll be back.
[BOSS 1A]
Wait a sec.
You're a hitman in Hakata now.
So be wary of the hitman killer.
[SAITO]
The hitman killer?
He's a hitman that only
kills other hitmen.
He calls himself
the Niwaka Samurai.
Why's he killing hitmen?
[BOSS 1A]
I got no idea, kid.
But I'm pretty sure
you'll be fine.
That one's probably got
bigger fish to fry. [laughs]
Thanks for the tip.
[BANBA] The mayor, an assassin,
and a fancy club.
Yamato. My wallet.
I'd like it back.
[YAMATO] Heh. Guess you're
not that oblivious.
So, what did you
wanna ask me about?
Could it be this?
[YAMATO] Yeah. I don't
recognize the suit.
But this fella--he
worked at Club Miroir,
so I bet that's where this was.
Interesting.
[YAMATO]
He was murdered this morning.
His girlfriend, too.
Hey, Genzo.
One more hit of
extra firm noodles.
Sure thing.
[BANBA]
Why?
[YAMATO]
I hate it when they fall apart.
[BANBA] Not that. Why did
the guy get murdered?
Oh.
From what I heard,
he skimmed 10,000,000 off
the club's profits and
when they found out,
they hired a hitman.
That club must have some
pretty shady backers,
if ya ask me.
[GENZO]
Here you go.
[YAMATO]
Thanks.
[LIN] This must've been
for the club worker.
So...
That cheapskate.
[YAMATO]
Thanks for the ramen!
Man, the plot to this
tale keeps getting
thicker by the minute.
I wonder if Enokida's
hearing all this.
Check this out.
What am I lookin' at?
This was a present from Enokida.
It's a GPS-equipped robo-bug.
He calls it the
"redback spider."
The little trickster's
always making
one odd contraption or another.
[BANBA] It's pretty neat,
but I gotta wonder
why he would give it a red back.
I mean, a plain old black spider
would just blend
right in, ya know?
But this guy--
it might as well shout at ya.
"I'm a venomous spider,
so swat me."
[LIN]
Don't screw with me!
Three thousand yen
is a goddamn joke!
I'm not the one who screwed
up, so gimme my money!
Hey! You listening to me?
We can't settle this
with a phone call.
I'm coming over right now.
Damn!
Stop right there.
Who, me?
[LIN]
You think I wouldn't notice?
You just touched my ass.
[sputters]
The next time
you're feelin' frisky,
why don't you to
think about this!
Piss off, before I kill you.
Mark my words, shemale,
I'll get ya back for this!
You'll pay for this, ya hear?
Wasn't even near your ass.
[STORE CLERK 1AA]
Thank you for shopping with us!
[SAITO] Can I really
do this? Kill someone?
[sighs]
[SAITO] "Desperately need
pitcher and shortstop."
"Newcomers to baseball welcome."
That might actually be enough
to get someone into baseball.
All right. I'll be the same.
[MIROIR MANAGER 1A]
You're a detective?
I understand that the
mayor came here one time.
I have a few questions
about the people
who came in with him.
Sorry, but I don't
remember anything.
'Kay. Well, thanks anyway.
[SAITO]
Come on, Saito.
Just keep it together.
Stay calm.
Can I really do this?
[doorbell rings]
Is he back already?
Wait, that doesn't
make any sense.
Why would he ring
his own doorbell?
A man and his daughter?
Yes?
[JIRO]
Hi, glad you're up.
Sorry about bothering
you so late at night.
My name's Tanaka. The two of
us just moved in downstairs.
For you!
We're giving all our
neighbors presents.
Oh. Well that's very
thoughtful of you.
And what's your name?
[groans]
Gotta say, for an adult,
he's really careless.
Now, why don't the
three of us go on a trip?
Murase Jun.
[LIN] You wanted the detective
dead and now he is.
It's not my fault he
beat me to the punch!
Pay me half at least!
Why would I, when you
had nothin' to do
with his death?
You admit you didn't, right?
You know what, for all
I know, he offed himself
'cause he heard I was comin'
for him and got scared!
You've got quite the ego, boy.
It wasn't really a suicide.
Someone did kill him.
A different hitman
got to him before you
'n strung him up.
You didn't even
consider that option,
which is why you'll
always be an amateur.
No one can call me an amateur!
[laughs] Right, my mistake.
Spare me from your
professional wrath.
But if you keep on runnin'
your mouth like that,
I'm gonna give ya
to the Niwaka samurai.
Right, the hitman killer
everyone's talkin' about?
Till I see him myself,
I say he's a fairy tale.
Now about my money--
[ZHANG]
If you're that starved for cash,
go and deal with him.
He was sniffin' around
my business today.
The man's a real eyesore.
Go make him disappear.
[HARADA]
I see. He is quite the handful.
At the rate he's going,
he could be caught any day.
Forgive me, sir, but perhaps
you should talk to him.
[HARADA] The problem
is he kills citizens.
Sir?
We know an organization
that does human trafficking.
Purchase women with
no ties to this country
and let him have them.
No missing persons reports
means no investigations.
[MUNAKATA]
Understood.
[BANBA humming]
Wha...?! You mean they
aren't even gonna kiss?
Talk about anti-climactic. Ugh!
[BANBA]
Who're you?
Guess you must be Banba Zenji.
Yeah, you're face
really is kinda horsey.
Well, that's a
pleasant introduction.
So what? You my long-lost kid?
Decent guess, but no,
you're just a man
I was hired to kill.
[gasps]
Now why did you go and do that?
I'm just tryin' to
stay alive is all.
You are a hitman, right?
Yeah. That's right.
And I'm no amateur either.
Thing is, I didn't actually
come here to kill you.
I've decided to try
and protect you instead.