[ZHANG] He was sniffin'
around my business today.
The man's a real eyesore.
Go make him disappear.
[LIN]
I don't think so.
I'm not gonna do
any more jobs for you
till I've been payed
what I was promised.
I'm on strike.
Is that a joke?
I can easily find someone else
to do the job, you punk!
[LIN]
Is that so?
Well then, go right ahead
and hire your scab.
Hope it's not someone
you're too fond of,
because I'll probably kill them.
Long story short,
I expect another hitman
to show up here soon.
And, when they do,
I'll kill them.
Don't worry. I'll keep you
safe while I'm at it.
Now if the boss decides to
pay up, that'll change things.
Sounds fair. Now
leave, would you?
Not only is he still here,
he's made himself at home.
[mumbling] I'll get you
back soon, Qiaomei.
Sleeping pretty deeply, too.
Must have a trusting soul.
Either that or balls of steel.
[MAN 2A screaming]
All right. Up and at 'em.
Sleep well, Murase?
[MAN 2A screams]
Oh. Don't mind that guy.
He tortured and killed
someone's cat.
We're avenging it,
at the owner's request.
Using precisely the same methods
that he used on the cat.
[MAN 2A screaming groaning]
[JIRO]
I'm an avenger, you see.
Can you think of someone who
might want vengeance on you?
[MARTÍNEZ]
I was supposed to decapitate him
at the end, right?
And also, he didn't have
a tail to cut off,
so I improvised a bit.
[JIRO]
Excellent work as always, Maru.
[MARTÍNEZ]
So, is this one next?
[SAITO muffled]
Wait, wait!
Yeah, but before that,
I wanted to ask him something.
It's in regard to the two
friends you had with you.
When you attacked and then
lynched that poor foreigner.
[gasps]
I'm not the guy
you're looking for!
My name's Saito!
I'm not Murase!
I was waiting in
his house because
I was hired to kill him,
just like you were.
I work for Murder Inc, I swear!
You mean you're a redrum boy?
That would explain the
stuff you had, but...
Yes.
My business card is
in my breast pocket!
Well, I'll be damned.
He's tellin' the truth.
[sighs]
But wait.
If we got the wrong guy,
where's the real Murase Jun?
[SHINO] Yeah, I might've
overdone it with the gunpowder.
Doesn't really matter.
When you've got the
cops in your pocket,
you can afford to be sloppy.
Hey there, Munakata.
Yeah, Yoshida Masaki,
Yamashiro Tatsuya,
and Murase Jun have
all been taken care of.
Yes.
I made it look like
a DUI accident,
as per our instructions.
Only a fool would think
this was an accident.
[MUNAKATA sighs]
So what?
Have the idiot son's
friends been dealt with?
Yeah, it was a real
chore, but it's done.
Good.
We're supposed to
buy him women now?
Those were the mayor's orders.
They're not to be questioned.
I'll talk to the organization
tomorrow morning.
[JIRO] Why don't you
take my business card?
If you ever need revenge on
someone, just give me a call.
I'll give you a discount, okay?
Jiro. Thank you,
I appreciate it.
[SAITO sighs]
I'm really in over my head here.
[phone vibrates]
What's wrong, Yamato?
Surprised you're up this early.
[LIN]
Hey.
Wherever you think you're
sneakin' off to, think again.
Come on.
You're not holdin'
me hostage here.
[LIN]
You're a mark.
It's too dangerous
for you to go outside.
Do you have a
death wish or what?
[BANBA grunts]
What's this about?
[BANBA] You're gonna
have to buy it for me.
The Fukuya brand.
No added coloring.
Excuse me? Seriously?
Go on. I'm out of
spicy pollock roe.
Huh? Why the hell should I?
[BANBA] Because you just said
I'm not allowed to leave.
If someone doesn't get it
for me, I'll starve to death.
You can eat something else.
There's no reason it has to be--
Spicy pollock roe is
a Hakata specialty!
You want me alive?
Well, life without spicy
pollock roe isn't life at all!
In trying times such as these,
I depend on my
number one soul food!
So, yeah, man. Pick some up.
If ya do that, I'll be
a well-behaved boy.
[LIN growls] All right, I'll go.
Just keep the door locked
and don't open it for anyone.
Ya got that?
Thanks, bud. You can
keep the change, okay?
[BANBA]
Now, then.
Why are there so many
different types of this stuff?
It's just spicy pollock roe.
[ENOKIDA]
His name's Lin Xianming.
His papers say he's from Taiwan,
but it looks like he was born
in a Chinese farming village.
Huh. That's interesting.
There's nothing on
the web that tells us
who hired him, but if we
judge from his history,
then, I would guess it's
a Chinese organization.
Could be the group
backing Miroir.
Last place I poked my nose in.
Yeah, if so, maybe your
friend can help us
name the guy who was
meeting the mayor here, eh?
Mm! The trail's heatin' back up.
[gasps]
Oh! Think I should mention.
This Lin Xianming guy, he's
about to get himself a shiner.
What the hell, asshole?
That look. I like it.
You've got the attitude
of someone that can fight.
You're not too bad.
Tryin' to take me out
before you go for him?
I accept your challenge.
Nope.
Actually, I was just hired
to give ya one punch.
Huh?
[MARTÍNEZ]
Later.
[LIN]
Hey, wait! Fess up.
Are you an assassin hired
by Zhang, or what?
Don't know who that is,
but the man who hired me
is an avenger.
Late last night.
Remember clockin' a club worker?
[MARTÍNEZ]
Yeah. He was the client.
You gave him a
punch to the face,
so that's what you got from me.
Avengers never do
more to the target
than was done to the
client. Oh. Actually...
This is just a part-time
gig, but my real job...
Torturer. Huh.
You got it.
Although business has been
on the slow side lately.
Need anyone messed up?
Ya gimme a call.
See ya.
[BANBA]
Yamato wanted revenge?
Yeah.
He came by this morning
to have me look the guy up.
Left the wallet he'd
swiped from him.
I was just wrapping
up that search
when you sent me a
photo of the same guy.
Crazy coincidence,
don't'cha think?
Well hey, I guess it
made your job easier.
[ENOKIDA] I'm guessing that
revenge has been exacted by now.
Hey, give this back
to him, will ya?
That'll make him
and Yamato square.
And tell him to
ditch his receipts,
I found him by
matching up the date
on them with
surveillance footage.
Sure, I'll let him know.
What's this?
[ENOKIDA] No clue.
I haven't looked into it.
Little sister maybe?
Huh.
Hi there.
[LIN]
You bastard.
Guess I should've known
you'd leave anyway.
Heh. Felt like hittin'
the bat cages.
Sorry, I meant
the batting cages.
But as you can see, I'm safe.
Well yeah, of course
you are. Know why?
The killer was waiting
here to ambush you,
but he found me.
My goodness.
Now, I wonder what
I should do with you.
I could cut off your
head and mail it
back to your prick of a boss.
That would send a message.
I'd rather you let him go.
Uh--
Huh?!
Yeah, run back on home!
Tell your boss I want my money!
That cocky bastard.
Didn't even have the courtesy
to send a professional.
Oh. By the way.
Did you get the food?
[growls]
[LIN]
Here.
Wait a sec, this roe
is from Fukusaya.
I explicitly told you
to get the Fukuya brand!
[LIN] Cry me a river,
what's the difference?
Gimme a break, I was
only off by two letters.
Two letters...
That's also the difference
between kissing and killing.
Whatever!
[BANBA]
Oh. You left your wallet there.
[sighs]
[ZHANG]
You useless moron!
You couldn't even
kill that brat?
Sympathies.
Guess we're both
having a rough day.
Sorry. Didn't intend
for you to see that.
Back to business.
You needed a woman, right?
She's a pretty one.
I was plannin' to have
her work at Miroir
before you called, but she
fit the bill for you so well.
As per your request,
she has no family here.
She could disappear
this very night,
and no one would bat an eye.
[MUNAKATA]
All right. Here's the money.
Eh. Why don't you hang onto it?
Nothing is free.
What do you want instead?
There's this kid who used
to be a hitman of mine.
I want your people
to rub him out for me.
[BANBA]
I know it's late, but,
I made us some breakfast.
Well, brunch.
Huh?
Thought you were craving
that spicy pollock roe.
Oh, I'm gonna eat that later.
Haven't made any rice yet.
Well. why haven't you?
Eating ramen for
breakfast is just--
What? Is there somethin'
wrong with it?
It's just weird.
And besides, I've always
hated tonkotsu ramen.
It's greasy. I can feel it
sitting in my stomach.
Okay, well are you still
gonna eat it, or aren't'cha?
Yeah, I'll choke
it down somehow.
Got a policy against
wasting food.
That's very noble of you.
[timer beeps]
[BANBA]
It's good to go.
Hey, Detective.
Have you ever been hungry
enough to eat off the ground?
Luckily, no.
Of course not.
[BANBA]
Well, let's dig in.
[LIN]
Sounds good to me.
It tastes good.
Don't it, though?
[YUSUKE]
Hey sleepin' beauty.
Hey now, don't look at me
like that, you bitch.
You're ruining that pretty face.
We're gonna play now, 'kay?
For a very long time.
[SHINO] So after a
lifetime of loneliness,
she ends up in that
piece of shit's bed.
Would you mind not playing
with grenades in here?
Fine.
[MUNAKATA]
Ivanov.
In exchange for the woman,
they requested us
to take on a job.
The mark's a former
hitman of theirs.
Will you do it?
[IVANOV]
All right.
[SHINO]
Killing a hitman, cool.
You'll be like
the Niwaka Samurai.
[IVANOV] I seem to hear
about this "Niwaka Samurai"
all the time, but what does
the "Niwaka" part refer to?
[SHINO]
Who knows?
Niwaka is a traditional
form of theatre
that's done here.
There's a specific mask
worn by its performers.
The killer got his name
because he wears such a mask
and because he wields a katana.
Although, according
to the rumors,
everyone who's seen him
has been murdered.
But if everyone who's
seen him is dead now,
then how does anyone know
what he looks like?
That's why they're rumors.
Rumors and nothing more.
[phone vibrating]
[SAITO]
Hello?
[BOSS 1A] Hey! Thought I'd
call to congratulate ya.
[SAITO]
Congratulate me for--?
[BOSS 1A]
For doin' the job on Murase Jun!
I saw that so-called
traffic accident.
Surprised the cops bought it.
Huh?
[BOSS 1A] I've already
sent your payment,
but check that ya got it, 'kay?
[phone ringing]
Hi. You've reached Bar Babylon.
Oh, Saito, how's it goin'?
[gasps] Murase Jun?
Yeah, he died at
four this morning.
Report says he was killed
in a traffic accident,
along with two passengers.
I was wondering if
you were involved.
At four AM I was
still with you,
so it couldn't've been me.
Yeah, wouldn't
really make sense.
Hey. Hang on a second.
You said two passengers
died as well?
[SAITO]
Yeah.
It looks like they were
all friends from college.
Same number of people
from the attack.
Huh?
[JIRO]
Oh. Nevermind.
At any rate, I didn't kill them.
Thanks, sorry to bother you.
[JIRO]
No, not at all. Call me anytime.
[SAITO] But if it wasn't
just an accident...
No way it was
just an accident.
[MISAKI]
Maybe to keep 'em quiet?
The attackers didn't
act on their own.
The victim said someone was
holding a camera, right?
Ah.
This is weird.
I wonder if I should
return the money or not.
Ah... Wha--?
You know what,
I deserve some fun!
Motsu hot pots're the best!
Iron gyoza is the best!
Tonkotsu ramen is the best!
Hakata is the best!
[giggling]
[SAITO]
Titty bars are the best.
[SPORTS ANNOUNCER 2A] ...catcher
just whiffed his throw!
The runner's past third now.
He's dashing for
home. He makes it!
Hell yeah!
[SPORTS ANNOUNCER 2A]
The runner from second's
passing third base now, too!
Will the ball make
it home in time?
No, it will not!
He's safe!
[SPORTS ANNOUNCER 2A]
...to an incredible two-run hit!
The Hawks have taken the lead!
In a game of baseball,
ya never know
what's gonna happen till
its the ninth inning,
and ya get two outs
and three strikes.
You know, I'm glad you got
the wrong spicy pollock roe.
This kind's got some
extra kick to it.
Don't you think?
It's really annoying when
they change the TV schedule
to work in sports.
[BANBA] So you're a hitman
that likes soap operas, eh?
Not for the reason
you're thinking.
It's just that, when you're
in this line of work,
sometimes it's nice
to get a glimpse at what
regular people's lives are like.
[BANBA]
Hm.
By the way.
Lin Xianming, right?
[gasps]
[LIN]
How'd you find out my name?
I looked you up.
[LIN]
Right, you are a private eye.
If ya don't mind,
I've got a few questions
I'd like to ask.
Would you mind
answering honestly?
[LIN]
Depends on the questions.
[BANBA] All right. Why did
you become a hitman?
Why does anyone?
It's a lot of fast money.
[BANBA] And you need it
'cause you're in debt?
Yeah. That's one way to put it.
And what if I said
I'd pay off your debt
in full right now?
Would'ja let me?
[BANBA]
Let's strike a deal.
You give me information.
And I'll pay you well.
Five million.
That's how much it would
take to get me free.
[BANBA]
Hm.
So will cash be okay?
[BANBA]
So, question one.
What organization hired you?
It was Kakyu.
They're a bunch of exiled Yakuza
who joined the Chinese mafia.
Ah. One of those multinational
groups that's on the rise.
Where's their money from?
Drug sales? Weapons? Maybe both?
[LIN]
People.
Human trafficking.
[LIN] I'm not directly
involved in that,
so I don't know the details.
They give names.
I hunt people down
and kill them.
All right.
Well, do you recognize the
back of this guy's head?
I've only seen him
once before, but yeah.
That's Longfang Wang.
He's the group's leader.
That's good to know.
Explains why the mayor didn't
want them seen together.
It'd be a scandal.
I've got a few more here.
Do you mind?
[LIN] It'll still depend
on the question.
Whoa, wait, why am I naked?
[gasps]
[SAITO]
Wait. No way.
Hey, uh. Sorry, but--
[SAITO]
Come on, come on!
She's dead. She's dead.
She's dead! She's dead!
[BANBA]
There you go. Five million.
Guess this means you're
a free man now.
What do you plan to do
with that freedom?
[LIN]
I'm going home.
Got somebody waiting
for you there?
Not a question I'll answer.
If you ever end up in trouble,
feel free to give me a call.
I'll be happy to help.
There's nothing you
can help me with
and no reason you
should want to.
You still don't
get it, do ya, kid?
Hey, what is it that a hitman
needs more than anything else?
What?
Prob'ly the strength to
overpower their victims.
Sorry, but no, you're
off by a long shot.
Here's a hint. It's something
you need in baseball, too.
I have no idea.
[door clicks]
[sighs]
Guy's a total weirdo.
[ZHANG] Heh. You finally
decide to apologize?
[LIN]
Hell no. I got my 5,000,000.
Oh?
I can pay off my debt now,
so I'm a free man.
Just callin' to tell ya
you can my ass goodbye.
[ZHANG] Ah, I guess you haven't
watched the news today.
Huh?
[NEWS REPORTER 2A]
A woman's mutilated body
was found this morning,
at a hotel in Fukuoka city.
The victim is believed
to be a Chinese student
who's been living in Fukuoka.
The woman's name
was Lin Qiaomei.
The police are currently
searching for a man
who was sharing the room with
her as their chief suspect.
No... Qiaomei...
[QIAOMEI] Brother! Brother!
Don't leave me, please!
[growls]
[ZHANG]
Sounds like you just found out.
Yup, that's your
kid sister all right.
She came on our books
three years ago.
And an excellent buyer showed up
right after you
went rogue on us.
If only you'd been a
little more cooperative,
we might've been able to work
out a joyous little reunion.
[LIN]
You're dead. I'll kill you both.
You and the bastard who
did this to my sister.
I'll slit your god damn throats.
[LIN]
Give me a name!
[BANBA]
Spicy pollock roe works.
[JIRO] Your avenger will
be dispatched shortly.
[BANBA]
Sure, I'll take that job.
[ENOKIDA] Of course, I wouldn't
show up empty-handed.
[BANBA]
People are so nosy here.