Yeah, right in the sweet spot.
This is gonna be a good day.
Hey. The blind pitcher.
Say what? Shut your mouth.
[BANBA]
You live in Kokura, don't'cha?
Why're you in my batting cages?
It's not like you own the place,
if you've got a
problem, then leave!
Unless you want me to pay
you back for last time!
Say what?
Oh, how 'bout you
pretend ya don't owe me?
You'd just slow me down!
Ha! That hit went
straight to shortstop.
Easy double play.
You shut your damn mouth.
Shit.
Ball.
Ball. Four in a row. Nice.
Or was it four hit-by-pitches
with the first up
strolling home?
Shut your mouth,
or I'll kill you!
With aim that lousy,
I don't think you can.
[BOTH]
What?
Damn it all. He's dead and gone,
so why can't I stop
thinking about him?
[knocking]
Can I help you?
Good afternoon.
I had an appointment with Zenji.
[LIN]
Have some tea.
[SAYURI]
Thank you.
[LIN] I just got off
the phone with him.
He's on his way right now.
His office looks
nicer than I remember.
It's clean. Can I assume
that's thanks to you?
[LIN]
Guess so. I tidied up a bit.
And I forced him to
put a bath in here.
No way am I gonna live somewhere
that doesn't have a bath.
So tell me.
How long have you
and Zenji been dating?
[LIN laughs] Since never.
I'm just a freeloader.
[laughs]
Say, didn't you
used to date him?
Yeah. Zenji and I
had a good run.
Now that said,
we only started dating because
I was hired to kill him.
[gasps]
Believe it or not, he's
settled down quite a bit.
He was a wild man
when I first met him.
He partied a lot in those days,
so it wasn't hard at
all to approach him.
You mean Banba was a party boy?
Girl you better spill it.
[BANBA humming]
He just had to show up now.
[BANBA]
Oh, hi, Lin, I'm back!
Say "welcome home."
Speaking of courtesy,
say hi to our guest.
How goes it, Sayuri?
You're early.
Actually, I arrived
right on time.
You showed up late is all.
[BANBA laughs]
Yeah, my bad.
I guess I forgive you.
Lin and I had a good chat
while we waited for you.
Right?
We sure did.
Uh... Well that's nice.
You kept the conversation
appropriate, right?
Oh, define "appropriate."
Let's get to business, yeah?
Here's your file.
[LIN]
What's all this?
Remember the Kakyu association?
This is a list of their execs.
Names and addresses.
'Kay. So, what now?
I think you can guess.
We're gonna murder the
bastards one by one.
Huh?
[NAOYA]
So, tell me, Lau.
Is it common in Hong Kong
to talk business
in this sort of setting?
Of course not, but I
don't quite know my way
around in Fukuoka,
and I wanted to make sure
that we could talk in private.
Oh, I see. So, the
Sheung Wan syndicate.
You're expanding.
Specifically, you plan to
start moving into Japan?
Yes. And since it
isn't too far from us,
we think Fukuoka is
a good place to start.
But first,
we'll need to deal
with a powerful group
that's based here.
[NAOYA]
The Kakyu association.
[LAU] Since their chairman
was just murdered,
the group's likely in disarray.
We plan to hit them before
they get their pants back up.
And I've heard that one of your
boys is a former insider.
The Submarine Ninja.
Did I hear right?
Yeah. They have a history.
Then how does this sound?
I'd like you to sign
with us exclusively.
We'll have to talk numbers,
but I'm interested.
Good.
But before that, we'd like
your man to prove his mettle.
If he's able to kill these
two men, then we're on.
They're both Kakyu executives.
[NAOYA] A test of our
abilities. Very well.
Oh, and more thing.
I hear the Submarine Ninja
is actually an old
baseball friend of
yours, and you went
to high school together.
Yes. Is that going
to be a problem?
No, not at all.
You're concerned that
my friendship with him
might present a
conflict of interest.
Not to be rude, but
personal attachments
can sometimes get
in the way of business.
That won't be an issue.
Be they friends of mine or not,
the assassins in my employ
are nothing more
than tools to me.
The first guy on our
hitlist is Unoyama Takashi.
Killing every single one
of their executives
sounds like a
serious undertaking.
Are you sure it's
absolutely necessary?
Well, Kakyu still has a hit
out on the Niwaka Samurai.
They're also after Sayuri,
since she took out Wang.
And don't forget,
you've been taking up
space on their hitlist
for a while yourself.
True. I doubt they'll forget
about us anytime soon.
[BANBA] Right? I'm just
tryin' to be proactive here.
And I could use some help.
[LIN] Fine. What do
you want me to do?
[BANBA]
First, change your clothes.
Huh?!
[doorbell rings]
Good evening, sir.
I'm Myoken Tatsuro, head
attorney at Myoken Law Firm.
And this is my secretary.
Kobayashi Noriko,
it's a pleasure.
Pleasure's all mine. Please sit.
[BANBA] My schedule opened
up sooner than expected,
so I thought I'd come by early.
I hope it's not any trouble.
No, not at all.
So here's my issue.
I've got some neighbors who're
threatening to sue
me over my dogs.
What they don't seem to
understand is that dogs bark.
--I mean--
--[BANBA gasps]
Something the matter?
[BANBA] No, sir, but isn't
that the craftmanship
of Taikei Naotane?
Forgive me, but could I
take a closer look perhaps?
By all means.
I see we both admire his work.
Wow. These are just amazing.
I quite agree.
I'll tell you, they
weren't easy to come by.
I'm sure.
Forgeries like these
are tough to make.
Huh?
No. He got the boss!
Shit!
Now that's a good secretary.
So efficient.
Feel free to give me a bonus.
So, who's next?
[BANBA]
A guy who lives in Nishijin.
Kim Byonghi.
[KIM]
What are you?
[SARUWATARI]
I'm an assassin.
[KIM]
You've gotta be kidding--
You'd think a high-ranking
mob guy could put up a fight.
Oh, right.
Make sure that you leave
something near the bodies.
To prove that it was your work.
Got it? Have fun
out there, okay?
[SARUWATARI]
The "Submarine Ninja" was here.
[SARUWATARI] Next up is Unoyama
Takashi down in Hakozaki.
What's going on here?
I can give ya three guesses.
[gasps] Kim Byonghi?
Yeah, he was a long time
Kakyu association executive.
The funny thing is
we were just on our way
to kill that guy ourselves.
Yeah, we were.
C'mon, guys.
Don't talk like that
in front of a detective.
[BANBA laughs] My bad.
Say, what was he killed with?
We haven't determined that yet.
Must've been sharp though.
Pierced right through his heart.
Someone stabbed him
through the heart?
[SHIGEMATSU sighs]
Also, we found a shuriken
[BANBA, LIN]
Huh?
Ah? The hell is this?
Katanas?
[MYOKEN]
Hello there. Sorry I'm late!
I'm Myoken Tatsuro, head
attorney at Myoken Law Firm.
Oh. Listen, I didn't
kill these guys.
Hey, wait!
[screams]
Damn it. Ah, whatever.
He seemed pretty straight-laced.
But I wonder how this'll
play out with the client.
[LEE]
Kim and Unoyama?
[SUZUKI] They were killed
in quick succession, sir.
And do we know who did it?
[SUZUKI] Our police sources
say that shuriken
were found near
both of the bodies.
Shuriken .
[LEE] So you're the
"submarine ninja"?
It's possible that
he's been taken in
by a rival organization.
Suzuki.
I need you to escort
the other executives
to a secure location.
Then eliminate anyone
in the organization
who seems suspicious.
I trust your judgement.
Sir.
We'll take revenge
against whatever group
is pulling the strings here.
I'll need to find a
hitman who can match
the Submarine Ninja's prowess.
In that case, sir.
I was recently
contacted by a handler
who isn't yet known to me.
He claims to represent
a Chinese hitman.
He says that he's
highly skilled.
I'm guessing you're Suzuki.
You look a little disappointed
to see that I'm so young.
No. I'm just surprised.
No need to worry.
I've been killing
for a very long time.
So tell me.
Will our initial
offer be sufficient?
Yeah. But I do have
one other condition.
I'm lookin' for this guy.
His real name is Maomei, but
he's prob'ly using an alias.
Ever seen him?
No. I haven't.
That's funny, 'cause I heard
that he was working
for you guys.
[SUZUKI]
One of our executives could
be employing him privately.
[FEILANG]
So look into it.
Find out where he is for me,
and I'll do whatever you want.
[SUZUKI]
Your terms are accepted.
But before that, we do need to--
[FEILANG]
Oh, yeah, lemme guess.
You're gonna want me to prove
I've got the skill
to get it done.
Just tell me someone
nearby you want dead.
[INFORMANT 10A]
Honestly?
I'm pretty freaked
out right now.
The way they were grilling me,
it's like they all knew
I'd been leaking info.
And all the executives have
gone into hiding somewhere.
Understood. I'll cut off
contact for a while.
You should try 'n lay low
until this blows over.
Just lemme ask ya
one last thing.
Someone must have been in charge
of evacuating those
high-level execs.
Did'ja hear who it was?
[SHOP OWNER 10A]
Thank you. Have a lovely day!
[whistling]
[LIN]
Feilang.
[shop door chimes]
Good evening!
Tell me.
How much did you
get paid to squeal?
[gasps]
I hope it was worth it.
[INFORMANT 10A groans]
[yawns] Thanks for coming.
[screams]
[LIN grunting]
[LIN]
I really trusted you, Feilang.
Y-You were always there for me.
[FEILANG]
Aw, buddy, you forgot.
The only person you
can trust is yourself.
You would make one lousy hitman.
You know that?
Go to hell, Mao.
[BANBA]
Hey, Lin. Wake up.
Lin.
[gasps]
Guess you were
having a bad dream?
You started yelling
in your sleep.
Yeah, sorry.
It's nothing you
should apologize for.
I'm goin' out for a bit.
Will you be okay here?
If you're going after Kakyu,
then I'll come with.
Nah. Tough luck.
They ended up reacting
faster than I thought.
There's no one to go after.
The executives went
into hiding yesterday.
I see.
[BANBA]
The trail's not cold yet though.
I'm gonna tail the guy they put
in charge of the evacuation.
His name's Suzuki.
A job like this'll
be easier to run solo.
I might need your help
again soon though.
If you're up for it.
Okay, I'm headin' out.
[sighs]
Say, "have a nice day."
It's not happening.
Shut up and go.
My little ice queen.
[LIN]
That's Banba's handprint.
He grabbed me hard enough
to make a bruise,
and I still didn't wake up.
I'm lucky that it
was someone I can--
[LIN]
What? Trust? You idiot.
I almost made the same mistake.
Let Feilang happen
all over again.
You can't trust someone
just because they're nice.
I don't know anything
about Banba.
His motives could be just
as rotten as the rest.
There's no way to know.
[LIN]
Just end it.
[door clicks]
[SUZUKI]
Good work last night.
Though ideally,
we'd have preferred it
if you'd taken a slightly
subtler approach.
Well, you didn't specify
how you wanted it done.
[sighs]
Ha! He's certainly
changed his appearance.
But that's Maomei all right.
So he goes by Lin Xianming now.
He used to work for an
executive named Zhang.
Not long ago,
he turned against Zhang,
killed him, and disappeared.
That's all the information
I was able to find on him.
This oughtta be enough
for me to work with.
Then I take it we have a deal.
Yeah.
I'll kill whoever the Kakyu
association wants me to.
So gross.
Yo, it's in. Can ya hear me?
Why, yes, I can.
How do ya like
my newest weapon?
I've named it the redback
spider transmitter.
[YAMATO]
It's got a good signal,
but I did not enjoy
putting it in my ear.
[ENOKIDA]
Got eyes on the target.
There's the backpack.
Okay. Sticky finger time.
[coin clatters]
[YAMATO]
Oh, sorry, bud. You okay?
Back off!
[YAMATO]
Fine.
[MAN 10A]
Oh, just a game token.
Mission accomplished.
I swiped the bag
just like you said.
So, uh. What's in it?
[ENOKIDA] Congrats, Yamato!
You're a hero now.
The savior of Hakata.
[YAMATO]
Huh?
The bag--it's full
of explosives.
That guy was about to plant
it at Nakasu-Kawabata station.
Huh?
[yelps, sighs]
[YAMATO]
Say that first next time.
[ENOKIDA]
I was hacking him for kicks
and found his plan in an
email he'd sent himself.
And Nakasu-Kawabata is basically
right in my backyard, ya know?
I don't want anyone
makin' a ruckus there.
What's up, Lin?
Wow. This is perfect timing!
I need a favor from ya.
[ENOKIDA]
What's with the suitcase?
Are you running from home?
[LIN] Dumbass! What the hell
are you talking about?
I don't have a home to run from.
Wait. You really
are running off?
Aw, what happened?
Did you and Banba
have a big fight?
Please just let me keep walking.
I can't, I'm too curious.
Why're you leavin'?
Are ya goin' through
a rebellious phase?
C'mon, don't'cha wanna
get it off your chest?
If ya don't, I'll have no
choice but to call pappy.
[phone vibrates]
What?
[NAOYA]
Sarucchi. Where are you?
Still in Hakata?
[SARUWATARI]
Yeah.
Glad to hear it.
I need you to head down
to the Hakata Wharf
as fast as you can.
Okay, but why? What's up?
[HENCHMAN 10C groans]
[NAOYA] It's a rush job from
the Sheung Wan syndicate.
Apparently, their drug
stash at the wharf
is under attack right now.
The hell? Do you have any
idea what you've done?
What? I followed orders.
You told me you wanted
Sheung Wan distracted.
That's because you know
it was them, right?
Who went after your executives?
Yes, that's possible,
but I gave you orders
to distract them.
Not to start a war!
[FEILANG]
Don't be a Nervous Nancy.
I'll finish what I started.
Oh, yeah.
I left two of 'em alive
for you to question.
Hey. The hell are you doing?
We need to leave now.
You don't mind if I take
some plunder first, do ya?
[FEILANG whistles]
All right, just make it quick.
[whistling]
Like I said, there was
something about it
that was just wrong.
[ENOKIDA]
Yeah but, how do you mean?
It's not a problem
with people like you
because your
objectives are clear.
You don't worry
about good or evil.
You're in it for the cash.
Aw, thank you for
the compliment, Lin
But Banba's not like that.
Which means I can't figure out
why he does what he does.
N' without that,
I'm way too vulnerable.
Oh. I get it.
So you ran away
because you're afraid
he's going to betray you.
You're thinking it'd be safer
to not give him the chance.
Shut up.
It's about more than me
having trust issues.
I just--
I was living a pampered life
there that I didn't deserve.
What's wrong with
getting pampered?
People in our line of
work don't get to die
pleasant deaths in our beds.
And no one deserves shit.
So why not just
embrace what life
throws at you and enjoy it?
You needed a favor, right?
What exactly do you
want me to do?
[ENOKIDA] Ah. Just hacked
the store's camera.
[LIN]
Who are we watching?
[ENOKIDA] He was our mole
at the Kakyu association.
But last night, he was murdered.
I kinda feel a
little responsible.
We have other spies
there, but still.
Huh.
I'm going to need
you to take care
of this assassin before he
can get to our other spies.
[LIN]
Gotcha. Sounds simple enough.
[gasps] Wait! Let me
see his face again!
[ENOKIDA]
Sure.
[FEILANG whistling]
What? No way.
[ENOKIDA]
Don't tell me you know him.
Yeah. It's really him.
My best friend Feilang.
It's been six years
since he killed me.
[SARUWATARI] I take it
you're the one who did this?
[FEILANG]
So what if I did?
[SARUWATARI]
I'll kill you.
Hm?
[FEILANG whistling]
[FEILANG]
Such a damn wet blanket.
In that case,
I'll destroy them.