[MAN 9A screams]
You know, boys like you
really are the worst.
Making promises of marriage,
then grabbing all
the cash you can.
And, why don't you explain
what you did after that?
Start talking.
Well, we hired
a man to attack her.
And then what?
We recorded it and
posted it online.
[yelps]
Say, what does it feel like
to completely betray someone?
Someone who trusted you.
[door clicks]
Hey, Lin, how was your night?
Come on, buddy.
That's where you say
"great, how was yours?"
Didn't they cover
this in school?
[LIN]
Nope.
[BANBA] You come home after
being out all night
without calling, and in a short
skirt like that, no less.
Where'd I go wrong?
So, first of all, stop talking
as if you're my mother.
And then try to remember
that not everything
in the world
revolves around you.
I had to work, remember?
Oh. D'ya mean with Jiro?
So you accepted his
offer. Good for you.
The Summer heat's been
kickin' Maru's ass.
[BANBA] It's kinda like
you're their pinch hitter.
Yeah, sure.
The guy we were hired to deal
with was a real shithead.
[SPORTS ANNOUNCER 9A] He hit
another two homeruns today,
making him the clear frontrunner
for this home run derby.
And tying him with his
own record from last year.
Man got 40 homeruns.
Pretty impressive.
Whelp. Time I
started catchin' up.
I'm off to the batting cages.
Why are you competing with pros?
I'll see ya.
Uh-- Could you get toilet
paper on your way--
Oh. Are we running out?
Pretty considerate of
you to let me know.
Thanks, roomie.
Oh, shut up, will ya?
Where's my "have a nice day?"
[LIN]
Just get outta here.
Fine, see ya later.
[door clicks]
So I'm getting considerate. Huh.
Prob'ly a side effect
of this... pampered life.
[thud]
You just need some time
to warm up a bit, right?
Oh, shut up.
And by the way if
you've brought me
another crap job,
you're in for it.
Am I now?
You're the one who
staged an assault
on our last client's base.
So it shouldn't surprise you
that clients are wary of us.
Bunch'a damn cowards.
Your shuriken are getting blunt.
They need maintaining.
They're the tools of
your trade, remember?
Who cares? They're disposable.
[NAOYA] That may be true,
but they still need
to be in good shape
when you use them.
You've always been
careless with your tools.
No matter what I'd say.
I wonder, did you oil
your mitt even once
back during our baseball days?
So did you come
here for a reason?
Yeah. I'm here to tell you
about our new contact.
They're with an
organization based
down in Hong Kong.
And they seem to be
well aware of our
troubled relationship with
the Kakyu Association.
Which could make this
quite interesting.
I have my doubts.
You haven't changed a bit.
Just have a little faith in me.
Hey, kitty. You want
some scratches?
You're kidding.
You haven't taught him our
signs yet? Why the hell not?
Well, 'cause I thought you
were planning to do it.
So when you say "signs"
you mean all this?
Exactly. Try this one.
That's how we tell ya
to steal a base.
But, how am I supposed
to remember it?
Once you know the key,
the rest is simple.
For us, everything starts
down at the belt.
All that matters
is what you touch
right after touching your belt.
Everything else is a fake out.
If I touch my belt
and then my ear,
I want you to steal.
But if it's belt, then hat,
you should bunt.
I think I get it.
[GENZOU]
Really?
I told you to do what?
To bunt.
[GENZOU]
Bingo!
Here's one for you.
If the chest is touched
after the belt,
that signals a hit and run.
Like a drive by?
[GENZOU, BANBA chuckle]
Here. It'll be faster
just to show ya.
Ah.
[yelps]
Oh, shit!
What're ya doin'?
You can't turn back!
Why not? He didn't hit the ball.
Doesn't matter.
When you get that sign,
ya gotta run like
he will hit it.
If you're busy watching him,
you'll get a late start.
But what if that
means I'm tagged out?
If it happens, then so be it.
Baseball's like that sometimes.
Jeez, is this sport a
pain in the ass or what?
Once you get the sign
for a hit and run,
just sprint on the
pitch and have faith.
'Cause the rest'll be in
the hands of your teammate.
So I'm putting my fate
in their hands, huh?
[gasps]
[HANDLER 9A] The only person
you can trust is yourself.
[GENZOU]
Lin.
If you're feeling out of it,
then go take a breather.
[LIN]
I-I'm fine.
Qiaomei?
[TRADER 9A]
C'mon, just think about it.
At least one of your kids
could have a decent life.
My answers no and that's final.
My children are going
to stay with me.
[coughs]
That's sweet.
But if you sold me
just one of 'em,
you'd have a much easier life.
You could even
buy some medicine.
Get out of here!
Leave at once!
Big brother?
It's all right. Don't worry.
There's nothin' to be
scared of, Qiaomei.
[QIAOMEI panting]
[QIAOMEI]
Brother!
Come back! Don't
leave me, please!
[LIN]
Qiaomei. Mom.
You can huddle closer
if you're cold.
It's not that. I'm just afraid.
'Cause I don't know what
they're gonna do with us now.
[BOY 9B]
From what I've heard,
your best chance of
living is to get sold off
to serve a rich family
Most anyone else'll just
wanna take your organs.
That's a lie! We're
going to school.
That's what Mom told me.
I heard that it's a
school for killers.
--What do you mean?
--[BOY 9C] He's a liar, too!
No I'm not. They're gonna
teach us how to kill.
Turn us from kids into
soldiers and hitmen.
And even that's better
than what some kids get.
[gasps, yelps]
Looks like a prison, doesn't it?
Apparently, it used to be one,
but now it's just a factory.
A factory that turns little
brats like you into killers.
[TRADER 9A]
Get out.
They wouldn't have
any space for you,
but one of their
trainees just died.
Be sure to work hard now.
[HANDLER 9A]
Hey!
C'mere.
Take note.
For as long as you train here,
you will treat my word as law.
Do you understand?
[HANDLER 9A]
For the next five years,
you're gonna be taught
how to survive.
Never rely on someone else.
The only person you
can trust is yourself.
That's the best lesson
you'll learn here.
Hell, it's the best lesson
you'll learn in your life.
So remember it.
[keys rattle, door clangs]
[GUARD 9A]
Get in.
I said get in!
[whistling]
[whistling continues]
Hey. Welcome home.
It's a pleasure to meet you.
I'm Feilang.
I'm Maomei. Same to you.
[FEILANG]
You'll be all right, Mao.
They rough you up?
No.
Well, when they do,
cry all ya want.
I won't make fun.
Though, I can't
really help either.
Around here, everything's
done in teams of two.
We'll be praised and
punished together.
So let's try and help
each other out.
You mean we're a team?
[FEILANG] Yeah, both in
study and in practice.
I had a partner before you,
but he killed himself.
[gasps]
[FEILANG] I woke up to find
him hanging right there.
I'm guessing it all got
to be too much for him.
Just goes to show,
we need to help each
other through this.
It's only five years.
Right? Partner?
[bell ringing]
--One here!
--Two here!
--Three here!
--Four here!
--Five here!
--Six here!
--Seven here!
--Eight here!
[HANDLER 9A]
Get up!
If you wanna eat
tonight, then run!
What the hell?
Don't think about it.
That's just how
things are done here.
But I--
[HANDLER 9A]
On your feet!
What's with that look?
You feelin' defiant?
[LIN growls]
[FEILANG]
We're very sorry, sir!
On my back. I'll carry you.
--[LIN] But--
--[FEILANG] Just do it!
So long as we're in this place,
we are two halves of a whole.
[FEILANG whistling]
[LIN] I'm amazed that you still
have the energy to whistle.
It's rough here,
but you get used to it.
I was wanting to
tell you, Feilang.
Thanks for the save earlier.
Don't sweat it, Mao.
So, hey, I'm curious.
How did you end up here?
There's not much to say.
We were poor. Mom was
sick and owed money.
[FEILANG]
So she sold you?
No!
I-I sold myself.
Lied to my mom about it.
Told her I'd gotten a job.
What made you do that?
No matter how poor we got,
Mom would never
give in to the man
who wanted to buy me and Sis.
She always tried to
protect us. And, well...
I guess I figured
that was enough.
My mom fought to keep me.
And knowing that,
I could do anything.
I see.
[LIN]
What about you?
My mother sold me flat out.
She worked as a hooker, see.
She tried using me to advertise.
But, uh. You can
guess how that went.
Ten year old boys aren't
the best at that kinda thing.
But, you know...
I'm actually glad I ended up
in this screwy place.
If you compare it to how
my life used to be,
it's an improvement.
That's why I'm determined
to make it out of this place.
No matter what I have to do.
[sighs]
[BOTH grunting]
[grunts]
[panting]
[HANDLER 9A]
Enduring the pain is not enough!
Endure the terror!
It's your fear that
makes you talk.
And once you talk, you're dead!
[yelps]
[TRAINER 9A groans]
[TRAINER 9B groans]
So the rankings are up.
Did you see 'em?
Yeah. You and me
were on top of it.
Say, Mao.
I've had something on
my mind for a while.
You wanna work
together after this?
It might not be
possible right away,
but once we've earned our
freedom, we can team up.
Make some money.
And figure out how
to enjoy our lives.
Sounds good to me.
Once we're workin' together,
we'll be unstoppable.
N' also,
once we're partners again,
you should come to my house.
So I can introduce
you to my family.
[LIN]
Somethin' wrong?
No, I'll be there.
I can't wait for it.
Thanks, Feilang. Really.
I wouldn't have made it
if it weren't for you.
Let's give this
final test our all
and pass it together.
[FEILANG] Yeah. We're finally
getting out of here.
Eh, partner?
[LIN]
That's right. The two of us.
[HANDLER 9A]
This is your final exam.
There's no time limit.
Whoever can kill his
opponent will graduate.
There's no way.
No. You're kidding, right?
Nothing's off limits.
You may use any of the
weapons we've provided.
Begin.
No friggin' way!
Let us outta here!
[HANDLER 9A] Should you refuse,
you'll both be disqualified.
Let us out, damn it!
[LIN yells]
Mao, wait. You really--?
[whispering] Fight,
Feilang! Pretend!
I'm gonna smash the
chains with an axe.
We'll fight our way out!
[LIN grunts]
[BOTH grunting]
One more hit should do it.
[yelps]
[LIN sputters]
Feilang... Why did you--?
[FEILANG] You're asking why?
Because I wanna win.
Do you remember
what I said to you
on the first day you came here?
About how the partner I had
before you killed himself.
Well, that was a lie.
That's right.
I killed him myself.
[grunts]
I overheard the trainers
saying what the final would be.
[LIN yelps]
[FEILANG] I thought having
my partner commit suicide
would get me out of
actually having to fight.
But no. Then you came along.
Sucks to be me, doesn't it?
[LIN yelps]
I really trusted you, Feilang.
You were always there for me.
Aw, buddy, you forgot.
The only person you
can trust is yourself.
You would make one lousy hitman.
You know that?
Go to hell, Mao.
[FEILANG screams]
[pants]
[yells]
I'll make it out of this place.
No matter what I have to do.
[screams]
Congratulations.
Each of you has passed
your final exam.
You've cast aside your humanity
and become full-fledged weapons.
Well done.
[BANBA]
Lin!
[gasps]
[BANBA]
Nice.
You daydreamin'?
Luckily, I have your back.
You're welcome.
[LIN] Yeah. Pampered is
the word, all right.
[BANBA]
That sure was fast.
[JIRO]
An employment exam.
[BANBA] A famous leader
in the Kakyu association.
[LEE]
The Submarine ninja?
[YAMATO]
Whew! Now that is fine!
[FEILANG?]
A katana?
[LIN]
It's over.
[BANBA] Feels like somethin'
good's gonna happen today.
[MAN chuckles]
I'm takin' the virus
now. You won't mind.
[FEILANG]
Shiny.
[phone vibrates]
[FEILANG]
Figure out where he is yet?
Japan? Hakata?
Got it. You can text
me the details.
[FEILANG]
Found you at last.
We'll be reunited soon, partner.