Holy crap. From this video...
...it really does look
like I killed her.
[gasps]
[SAITO]
Bar Babylon.
[NEWS REPORTER 2A]
We've obtained newly released
security camera footage
from the scene of the crime.
This man is being sought
as a person of interest--
Guess our ploy worked.
[REIKO] If there's a hell,
we're all gonna see it.
Hey. Who the hell're you?
[HENCHMAN 3D groans]
Shit!
Don't kill me.
[gunshot]
Tell me who you sold her to,
and I'll make your death
slightly quicker.
[ZHANG] Heh. Some rich psycho
with a fetish for cutting.
That poor, helpless girl.
Bet he toyed with for a while.
That isn't what I asked you!
Just give me a name.
[ZHANG] Heh. While I'm at it,
lemme tell ya one more thing.
That sweet mother
of yours got sick
and died five years ago.
And that money you've
been sending home
like a good son? It's gone
right into my pocket.
You bastard!
You never stood a
chance at killing me,
because you are not
a professional assassin.
You're just a murderer
that gets paid.
Now the man who's
about to strangle you--
that's what I call
a professional.
You son of a bitch.
Do clean up when you're done.
It's no use.
That knife would only be
effective if I could feel pain.
[yells]
[screams]
[IVANOV]
How many of those do you have?
Go on and stab me, it won't
change how this ends.
[LIN] They make guns in all
shapes and sizes these days.
A real pro should know that.
[door clicks]
[BANBA]
Whew.
Damn, did I show up in
the nick of time, or what?
No need to thank me.
I'm a natural hero.
You're a real guardian angel.
How did you know
where I was, anyway?
[chuckles]
The "redback spider"
surveillance bug,
now equipped with GPS.
I put it on ya when I tucked
ya into bed last night.
And...
...now it's gonna
go on comrade Lenny.
'Kay. Let's ditch this joint.
Who the--
We really don't have
time to dawdle.
Wanna ride piggyback?
Can it, you. I can
walk just fine.
I don't get why
you're helping me.
People are so nosy
here in Hakata.
No time to cry yet.
I am not crying.
[JIRO] So you woke up
in a hotel bedroom,
with a woman you'd never met
before dead beside you.
Yes.
I have a vague memory of
being invited up to the room
by a beautiful woman, but,
that wasn't the girl I
woke up with this morning.
She seemed a lot younger.
Sounds to me like
someone set you up.
[SAITO]
What?
Someone else killed her
and then framed
you for the deed.
The woman who lured you up there
must've been an accomplice.
Aw, really?
I should've known I wasn't
cut out for a city like this.
How'd I ever think
I could be a hitman?
To be honest, I was
wondering about that myself.
How did a clean-cut
kid like you end up
workin' for Redrum?
Well, you see. One time, I...
I came close to killing someone.
[SAITO] The catcher told me
to throw a beanball.
But I chose to aim for his head.
He lived, but at the time,
it felt like murder.
So when I interviewed
with Murder Inc.,
I told them that exact story.
And to my surprise,
they hired me.
I think I get it.
Sounds like they must've
taken that mistake of yours
as evidence of
a killer instinct.
Ever since that day,
I haven't been able to
throw a ball to anyone.
So there's no way I could
kill people for a living.
[gasps]
Hey, Jiro. You deal with
cases like this, right?
As an avenger?
Yeah.
[SAITO]
Then take revenge for me!
Huh?
Please frame the
people who set me up!
Make them pay for what they did!
[JIRO] Your avenger will
be dispatched shortly.
I have to say, I'm disappointed.
See, when you told me
you would handle this,
I thought you'd send your best.
[HENCHMAN 3E]
Hey, Zhang. Check it out.
So the punk had help.
I'll kill them both.
It's time I brought out
the best hitman in Hakata.
I'd appreciate it if you
gave us another oppurtunity.
This failure of ours...
We can't allow it to stand.
I'll let you try,
but I'm hedgin' my bets.
Also, your objective has
changed from kill to capture.
I wanna be there when they die.
I understand.
[gasps]
[door creaks]
Oh. G'morning, sunshine.
You ready for breakfast?
It's Tonkotsu Ramen,
your favorite.
Did you patch me up yourself?
[BANBA]
Nah, I'm friends with a doctor.
You should take
it easy for a bit.
[BANBA]
You goin' somewhere?
Of course I am.
My little sister was murdered.
I'm going after her killer.
I can't fault you
for that. Know his name?
I'm expecting this to
give me some leads.
[BANBA] So, you n' your knives
are gonna hack the thing,
get an address,
and limp on over, eh?
You act like you can handle
anything by yourself, Lin.
But that isn't how
human beings survive.
Like I told you this
morning, I can help you.
Then "help me" find
the person responsible.
Find the psycho who
cut up my sister!
There ya have it.
Guess you're nothin' but talk.
[BANBA]
Spicy pollock roe should do.
Huh?
I'll take the job, and my pay
will be in spicy pollock roe.
Five years supply!
[phone vibrates]
[YUSUKE]
Hey there, ol' pal!
When's my next girl
coming? I'm lonely.
[MUNAKATA]
I'm busy. Ask me later.
[YUSUKE] Ah? Look, if you
can't provide, I'll--
Human beings aren't
easy to come by.
We'll see what the
broker has in stock.
Do not find your own.
I'll call you.
That little shit.
Can't even keep his
pants on for a day.
You only ever get like this
when you're upset with yourself.
If you're blaming yourself
for Ivanov's death,
then stop.
The hitman named Lin.
He's far more capable
than we assumed.
I'm starting to wonder if
he isn't the Niwaka Samurai.
That's impossible.
The Niwaka Samurai would
never use a bullet.
[MUNAKATA] He is real.
I saw him once. Years ago.
[cackling]
[gasps]
[REIKO]
So that's how you lost it?
He was in my sights,
but I couldn't move.
I was paralyzed by his
intent to kill me.
I suddenly realized
that I'm afraid to die.
It's why I joined
the mayor's employ.
I thought it would be safer.
[MUNAKATA]
Despicable, aren't I?
[REIKO]
Heh. Not to me.
[ZHANG] My organization has
a job for the Niwaka Samurai.
And my sources tell me
you can contact him.
[GENZOU] Yeah well, your
sources told you right.
But his prices are pretty steep,
and he's extremely selective.
Do ya still want me to ask?
This is a matter
of our reputation.
So we'll be sparing no expense.
Well, in that case,
I'll talk to him.
Who's the mark?
[SHIGEMATSU] This is our
prime suspect, Ito Takuya.
Last night, it seems he was
havin' the time of his life.
He hit every gentlemen's
club, cabaret,
and shake joint in town.
What's a gentlemen's club?
Place where you
pay to touch boobs.
Then what's a cabaret?
Place where you
pay to touch boobs.
And a shake joint?
Place where you
pay to touch boobs.
So they're all the same.
Now, all of that was legal.
The question is,
what did he get up to
after he entered this hotel?
Something doesn't check out.
There were two previous
victims with similar wounds,
but in those cases, the
bodies were dumped outdoors.
Not left in a hotel room.
Also, the guy's new to town.
He just moved to
Fukuoka for his job.
When the first two
killings occurred,
he was still in Tokyo.
Then...
It's possible this
guy was just framed.
[SHIGEMATSU]
Hey, Banba.
Sorry, but...
Are you and this girl, uh...
You know, are you
an item or somethin'?
Fill me in.
I think you're confused.
See, I'm a dude.
[SHIGEMATSU]
Oh. Hey, I'm all for that.
That's not what I--
Yeah. See? I said
to take it easy.
Why the heck aren't
you correcting him?
Whoa, sugar britches,
he already knows.
Shigematsu's just havin'
a bit of fun with ya.
So you're the guy.
Lin Xianming, the hitman.
Got a lot goin' on, huh?
Of course his friends
are like this.
All right, Banba, what does
mister mushroom head do?
This is Enokida.
He's a very
resourceful informant.
I'm glad you could
make the trip out.
Thanks again.
Yep. One house call a year.
Here. You can have it back now.
[gasps] Did you
find out who it is?
[ENOKIDA]
Mm... I dove in pretty deep,
but there wasn't much
of use to be found.
[ENOKIDA]
Don't make that face just yet.
I wouldn't have come out here
if I didn't have
something to show.
[ENOKIDA] This is security
footage from the crime scene.
The camera was
supposedly broken,
so the footage never
went to the cops.
But for some reason, it's
still in the hotel server.
First, the moment when
Ito Takuya arrived.
Check out the woman
with him. Familiar?
Is that--?
Yup. The mayor's
lethal secretary, Reiko.
Then, 30 minutes later...
We see another old friend.
That guy...
[ENOKIDA] Pretty big case
he's got with him, huh?
Almost like he's transporting
a person in it.
So she might've
already been dead.
And you say that woman
works for the mayor?
If he's the one who
did this, then--
Well, let's not get
ahead of ourselves.
Next, I'd like to play you
an interesting conversation.
It was recorded by
the red-back spider
Banba put on the Russian
gorilla's corpse.
[YUSUKE]
Hey there, ole pal!
When's my next girl
coming? I'm lonely.
[MUNAKATA]
I'm busy. Ask me later.
[YUSUKE] Ah? Look, if you
can't provide, I'll--
[RIEKO] Human beings
aren't easy to come by.
We'll see what the
broker has in stock.
Do not find your own.
[ENOKIDA]
The mayor has a single son.
He's a college student
named Harada Yusuke.
His official record is sparkly.
But from what I was
able to dig up,
this kid should
definitely be in prison.
So the mayor's been
covering it all up.
[LIN]
All right.
This Harada Yusuke
is the shitbag
who murdered my little
sister. I'm sure of it.
Hey, mushroom. Do you
know his address?
[ENOKIDA] Hm. I'm sure
I could look into it.
But you can bet your
pretty little stockings
that it'll have
some good security.
It might be tough
to storm the place.
[LIN]
I have a plan.
Huh?
In that recording, they said
they were gonna
buy another girl.
Well, what if they
bought me instead?
[gasps]
[LIN] For the plan to work,
someone has to play the broker.
Banba, do you think
you can you help me?
[sighs] How can I say no?
Can you find out when
and where they're doing
the deal, Enokida?
[ENOKIDA]
No problem
I'm gonna have to get dolled up.
[phone vibrates]
[BANBA]
Hey, old man.
What's this important business
you wanna talk about?
I've got a lot goin'
on right now.
Any of it have to do with
the Kakyuu Association?
[GENZOU] I just got a call
from them about a job.
They have two targets.
The first is a hitman
who used to work for them
called Lin Xianming.
The other is a private eye
they say teamed up with him.
Someone named Banba Zenji.
Oh, boy.
[GENZOU]
That's not the worst of it.
They're asking me to put
my best man on the job.
That's the Niwaka Samurai.
Now, the last thing I want
to do is get you killed.
But even if it's not through me,
they'll find him in time.
So, Banba.
Should I make an exception,
or do you want me
to treat this like
any other request?
Just go for it.
Give him the job.
Are you sure?
You heard me say you're
the target, right?
What do you plan to do?
[BANBA]
Maybe I'll just play dead.
[whispering] Be quiet.
You and I are gonna
have a quick word.
[ENOKIDA grunts]
That hurt.
There's no need to
be so rough, man.
I promise I'm not as
beaf cake as I look.
What happens here next will
be completely up to you.
You seem a bit less
than surprised.
Do you know what
brought us here?
Let's see.
When I turned on the
smartphone belonging
to your dead Russian friend,
it's GPS lead you
to this internet café.
You then looked at enough
security camera footage
to deduce that I must be
Banba's informant. How'd I do?
If you want this to
be your line of work,
then you should really try
to be a little more innocuous.
Say, have you ever wondered why
the redback spider has
that marking on it?
If they were just
a bit less visible,
people wouldn't kill
them half as much.
But redbacks want
to stand out.
It's like they're daring
us to screw with them.
You have to admit, it's a
badass way to be, right?
They rock! And we roll.
Keep it down.
Now tell us where
Detective Banba is.
There's really no need.
Why don't you hang out for
a bit and he'll come to you.
What are you saying?
As a professional informant,
I typically sell
this kind of info.
You do understand who has
the upper hand here right?
Fine, but you owe me.
Lin Xianming is planning
to take revenge
on the mayor's son
for killing his sister.
His sister?
[ENOKIDA] Banba Zenji,
intends to help him.
So that's what you meant
when you said he'd
come on his own.
On what day? What time?
Actually, that's completely
up to you guys.
[BANBA]
Dr. Saeki, you here?
Oh, Banba.
Not used to seeing
you twice in a day.
I know. Thanks again
for helpin' out.
Bringing a stab victim to
a cosmetic surgery clinic...
You really are an odd one.
--So, what can I do for y--?
--[JIRO] Ha, ha, hi, Banba!
How goes it, Jiro?
What're you doin' here?
Don't you know?
Why does any affluent
woman of taste, come here?
To be beautiful--
[DR. SAEKI] Jiro came to
donate a body. To "science."
Hey. Why spoil the fun?
The body. What's it look like?
[JIRO] Not sure what
you're looking for,
but knock yourself out.
Say, while I've gotcha here.
I wanted to ask you about this
revenge job I just accepted.
Yeah? Ask away.
[phone vibrates]
Hey, what's up?
Ya find out when the
exchange is happening?
[WOMAN 3A] It had the texture
of like, an old string bean.
[WOMAN 3B]
Ew, stop talking about it.
[BANBA] Oh, you are gorgeous!
Fashionable, too.
I know. I pulled
out all the stops.
Well, what about me?
Do I look like a mobster?
Try creepy drunk
uncle at a wedding.
Beauty is so cruel.
Let's get moving. We don't
have much time left.
[BANBA sighs]
You sure you wanna do this?
We can still leave. This plan's
too risky for my taste.
Even if you manage
to kill the son,
you won't get out
of there scott free.
All I care about
is seeing him dead.
If I end up getting
killed after, so be it.
I'm not gonna send
you to your death.
We'll find a way to get
you out, okay, tutz?
Oh, piss off.
[BANBA]
A good luck charm.
Call me if you need anything.
I'll come running.
My gallant knight.
[SHINO] So, the promised
goods are inside?
'Course. Wanna see for yourself?
[SHINO] What, out here?
That's not necessary.
[BANBA]
Well, then.
[SHINO]
Our business is done.
Tough break, Lin.
Apologies.
But, hey. Good luck.
[ZHANG]
You got sold out.
[LIN]
I found you, shitbag.
[GENZOU]
It might be the first time
the Niwaka Samurai
misses a mark.
[JIRO]
Hi! I'm an avenger.
[LIN]
The hitmen killer, eh?
[GENJO]
All right! Let's do this!
[LIN]
We're already there?
[SHINO] We've delivered
the goods as promised.
I hope this makes up
for past mistakes.
Well, fancy seein'
you again. Lin.