[FEILANG grunts]
--[SARUWATARI] Huh?
--Way too slow.
[SARUWATARI gasps]
[SARUWATARI grunts]
Ha. Damn amateur.
[SARUWATARI growls]
[SARUWATARI gasps]
Heh. Like hell I am.
[SARUWATARI yelps]
Why'd you have to go
and spoil the mood?
I think you've played
enough for today.
Come on.
[gasps, coughs]
[SARUWATARI] Shit, I never
learned how to swim.
Damn it.
[gasps, coughs]
[BANBA] Oh, ho, ho! It looks
like I caught a big one.
[SARUWATARI]
Banba? Wha...?
So, what, have you taken up
stalking me as a hobby?
What the hell are you
doing out here?
I'd like to ask you
the same thing.
What's new? What'cha
gettin' up to?
Oh, bite me.
Not a chance in hell
I'm tellin' you that.
Suit yourself. I'll get
out of your way.
Lemme just take this back.
Sarucchi?
Don't tell me ya drowned. You--
[SARUWATARI] How do ya like
that, ya cocky little--?
[BANBA] Nice, way to thank
me for saving your life!
[SARUWATARI]
Screw you!
[BANBA]
What's your deal?
[ENOKIDA]
I see.
So, you were put
through virtual hell
at an assassin
training facility.
Then forced to kill your
partner and best friend.
Yeah.
[ENOKIDA] But now it turns
out he's still alive.
What do you think about that?
About what?
How does your old
partner's survival
make you feel?
Happy, sad, afraid?
I dunno. I'm really
just confused.
Maybe you missed
him all this time.
You were best friends right?
Let's say I hired you
to murder him for me.
Do ya think you could do it?
I don't know.
Fair enough.
I'll go ahead and ask someone
else to deal with him.
But putting all that aside.
Your former partner and friend
that you supposedly
killed just showed up
in your new hometown
out of the blue.
So if you ask me,
that's not just a coincidence.
[FEILANG] You're in the Kakyu
Association's headquarters.
Trapped in a cell that very
few people leave alive.
Must feel hopeless, huh?
I'll give you one
chance to get out.
[FEILANG]
You have to fight to the death.
--[gasps]
--[HENCHMAN 10E] What?
[FEILANG] And whoever
survives will go free.
Are you insane?
There's no way that
we could do that!
Of course you can.
I mean, your lives
do depend on it.
Someone's gonna die.
The only real question is,
who's it going to be?
[NAOYA]
How'd you end up soaking wet?
I saw somebody drowning
and jumped in.
Huh? Wow, man, I'm surprised
you both didn't drown.
You used to wear
floaties in swim class.
Shut your mouth.
That was uncalled for, Sarucchi.
It looks like The Kakyu
Association is beginning
to get pretty bold.
They felt confident to attack
us even with you around.
Okay, look.
Your men were all dead
when I got here.
Not all. There's still
two men unaccounted for.
[HENCHMAN 10D]
I'm here, Lau.
So what happened?
Did you see the attack?
The Kakyu association
took us hostage.
Did you escape then?
N' what about--
[LAU]
Don't tell me...
[HENCHMAN 10D]
I'm sorry. They made me do it.
Damn that redheaded bastard.
What's he playin' at?
Hey, you. Tell us
where they are.
I'm gonna go make some
bodies of my own--
[LAU]
Wait!
No.
We will make no counterattack.
Huh?
Why the hell're you
changin' the plan now?
[LAU]
The situation has changed.
They're much stronger
than we thought.
[FEILANG] I killed a
Sheung Wan Exec in Beijing
a while back. I was
hired to do it by a large
and influential organization
based in Shanghai.
I took that ring off his body.
And when they see it,
they'll know the hitman
who killed their
exec is now with you.
Now what do you suppose
they'll make of that fact?
They'll think we formed an
alliance with that group.
Which would mean
they're outnumbered.
Hit the nail on the head.
They'll be terrified
at the thought
of our non-existent backup.
[phone vibrates]
[SUZUKI]
Lee. Has something happened?
Sheung Wan just informed
me that they would like
to discuss a cease fire
Will you accept it?
Right. Understood, sir.
Tonight it is. I'll be there.
See? My plan worked out.
Which means now, it's your
turn to do something for me.
And what do you want?
I need some information.
On around a 100,000 of this
fine city's residents.
Ugh. Sure could use
a shower right now.
I guess I might as well ask.
You took out Unoyama, right?
And you killed an
executive named Kim.
Yeah, but only because
I was hired to.
By who?
I can't tell you.
'Kay. That's all right.
At any rate, it sounds like
our interests are aligned.
That redhead I brawled
with. Know who he is?
No. You'd know more than me.
But I'm guessing he's
the Kakyu association's
newest hitman.
He's strong. So don't
underestimate him.
Feels like everything's
about to get dangerous again.
That's odd.
[BANBA]
Lin took all his stuff out.
[phone vibrates]
Hey, Banba. How are ya?
Huh? Lin's gone?
Nah. Can't say I've
seen him today.
No problem, buddy.
Yeah, you, too.
He asked me to pass
a message on to you
if we run into each other.
He doesn't understand what
the note you left meant,
so you should give him a call.
He really is a moron sometimes.
[LEE] As outlined in our
agreement, Sheung Wan will not
encroach on any
of Kakyu's territory.
And our syndicate will
make no efforts to hinder
any of your dealings or
developments in the region.
Are these terms acceptable?
Yes they are.
I find your terms
perfectly agreeable.
[LEE] We do have one
more small condition.
The "submarine ninja"
you've employed.
I would ask that you allow us
to take him into our custody.
In exchange, we're prepared
to hand over the hitman
who attacked you at the harbor.
You wish to avenge your
comrades, do you not?
You have a deal.
[MAN 11A whimpering]
Please, sir, you don't
have to do this!
'Course I don't.
[MAN 11A groans]
[sighs]
[DR. SAEKI] Oh. Fancy running
into you here, Lin.
[LIN] Dr. Saeki, I'm
surprised to see you here.
Do you need something
from the mushroom?
Not quite. Just
thought I'd stop by.
Oh, say, Lin. Why
don't'cha have this?
It's a skin care lotion
we promote at the clinic.
And it really does work.
Plus it's nice and compact.
For when you're out and about.
All right then.
I hope you end up liking it.
See ya.
Thank you. Goodnight.
[YAMATO]
Oh, hey, Lin.
[LIN]
Yamato.
Glad I ran into you.
Hey, I tell ya what.
Have these coupons.
They were in a wallet I
lifted from some asshole.
Fifty percent off
on any purchase!
That's a steal.
Thank you, but I'm good.
[YAMATO] Just take them.
Money is everything.
Later!
What's going on?
Yo, Lin!
[LIN] Why the hell're all
of you showing up here?
It's nice to see
you, too, buddy.
Even though you're rude.
I see that you're
surfin' the web.
Do ya want me to show ya
a couple dirty sites?
That's okay.
I highly doubt we're
into the same stuff.
That's enough of that, boys.
Not in front of Misaki.
Here. This is for you.
[LIN]
Uh. Really?
[JIRO]
Hakata Torimon buns.
I bought them as part
of a revenge job.
But, I didn't end up using them.
They're pretty good.
Hope you like 'em.
Take care.
Running from home is lame
Damn you, mushroom!
You promised not to tell anyone
I was planning to leave town!
You only had me promise
not to tell Banba.
You didn't say not
to tell anyone else.
[growls]
I know it's hard to believe,
but I think they're
all worried about you.
[LIN] They just showed
up to make fun of me!
[SAITO] Oh, Lin. Fancy
running into you here.
Did'ja get me a present,
you asshole? Huh?
What the--?
Wait a sec. Are you mugging me?
Oh. Yeah, Saito's the only
person I forgot to tell.
Huh?
[phone vibrates]
[ENOKIDA]
Huh, looks like someone else
is worried about you,
too. Pick it up.
[phone vibrates]
Hey. Shigematsu. 'Sup?
Oh, yeah?
You want me to give
the phone to him?
Not a problem. I'll put him on.
[SHIGEMATSU]
Lin. Can I run something by you?
What is it?
We had a weird set of
homicides last night.
Two men named Hayashi
Noriaki were murdered
in separate incidents.
[LIN]
And?
The thing is,
both of their names were spelled
the way that you spell yours.
Uh--
[SHIGEMATSU] It was a
73-year-old in the Chuo Ward
and a 30-year-old in Sawara.
They had nothing in common
aside from their names
and the way they were killed.
Both were attacked
with a large knife,
and had their left eyes cut.
[gasps]
[SHIGEMATSU]
You have any idea what this is?
Sorry, but I don't.
[SHIGEMATSU]
All right, well, be careful.
Sorry to bother you, Enokida.
[ENOKIDA]
No problem! Talk to ya later.
This the work of
your former partner?
Yeah. It was Feilang.
The last time I saw him,
I slashed his left eye.
There's no doubt.
He murdered them to
send me a message.
He's followed me here
'cause he wants revenge.
Yeah? So what are you gonna do?
I'm gonna go and see him.
Enokida.
I need to know which Hayashi
Noriaki he'll target next.
Can you help?
As if there's information
that I can't find out.
Just leave it to me, old pal.
Sheesh, Lin. Where did you go?
--[clatter]
--Oh, uh...
[LEE] I'm glad you could
make it. Sit, please.
You've done some
very impressive work.
I think we'll have a long
and productive relationship.
I'd like to propose a toast.
Sure.
To our newest partner, Feilang.
Oh, yeah?
Smells like betrayal.
--[BOTH gasp]
--[FEILANG] Don't be stupid.
[SUZUKI]
Lee.
Bastard!
The hell are you doing?
Nothing you would have
any right to blame me for,
considering that you
just tried to poison me.
And anyway, the virus I just
gave your boss can be cured.
You infected me?
It's an extremely lethal virus
developed by Sheung Wan.
I nabbed a vial back in Beijing.
It lies dormant in
the body for a week,
but once that week is up,
there'll be no way to save you.
[LEE gasps]
[SUZUKI] And where's this
cure you spoke of?
Don't worry it's hidden.
And I'll give it to you.
That's assuming you
do exactly as I say.
Wow, this hitman
is pretty clever.
[FEILANG]
So tell me, why the poison?
I thought I was doing
good work for you guys.
We made a deal with
the Sheung Wan executive.
One of the conditions
was that we give up
our new hitman for theirs.
But we couldn't risk you
joining up with them.
I could see that.
You know, the other
side's prob'ly thinking
the exact same thing.
Ugh. Damn it all.
I wanna kill the bastard.
There, there, Sarucchi.
Don't let it get to you.
It's over now.
Despite our best efforts,
Sheung Wan has given up
on moving into Hakata.
There's nothing we can do
about it, so let it go.
I'm talking about that
stupid carrot top.
I'll let this go just as soon
as I've slit his throat.
Yeah, yeah. For now,
let's just eat.
Dinner'll be on
me tonight, okay?
[NAOYA]
Hello. This is Naoya.
Yes. He's sound asleep,
as per our plan.
I'll see you shortly.
[ENOKIDA]
Ah! Found it.
The Hayashi Noriaki's had
two things in common.
Their names.
[ENOKIDA] And the fact
that they both bought
health supplements from
the same website.
Huh? Hey, I've bought some
stuff from that website.
I didn't feel any healthier,
but I did start getting
a whole bunch of calls
from telemarketers.
Heh, heh. That means they're
selling their customer's
contact information on the sly.
The Kakyu association must've
been one of their big buyers.
That's how Feilang
got their names?
And let's see here.
There we go!
There's only one
remaining guy named
Hayashi Noriaki with
an address in Fukuoka.
--And there it is.
--[phone vibrates]
Enokida.
Go ahead and text me
that address now.
I owe you.
Good morning, Sarucchi.
You sure slept well.
Naoya. What's going on here?
Part of our deal with
the Kakyu association
was that we give you up to them.
Lau didn't think
you'd like that.
So he had me drug
you last night.
Huh?! What did you just say?
[NAOYA]
We're giving you to the Kaky--
Naoya! You sold me
out, you bastard!
I'll kill you!
My. Such a temper.
[LAU]
Change of plans.
Looks like you're
the one about to die.
[NAOYA]
Hm? Hold on a moment.
I thought the original plan
was to hand him
over to them alive.
[LAU] There's a risk
that he'd switch sides
and become a danger to us.
It's just good business.
Loose cannons aren't safe.
This is not what we
had agreed upon.
Inside that case, you'll
find a little extra.
And, hey. You said it yourself.
Hitmen are nothing more
than tools, right?
[sighs]
That works for me.
Not the first time I've
had to sell a tool.
And for a price like this,
I can't complain.
Bastard!
It's a cut-throat business.
I'm sorry, Sarucchi.
You think sorry's gonna cut it?
You piece of shit!
What the hell?
[HENCHMAN 11C]
Bastard!
[groans]
[NAOYA]
Surprised I hit 'em all.
The recoil on this thing
is serious. Kinda hurts.
Okay. We're good to go--
[NAOYA]
Should've seen that coming.
Hell yeah, you should've!
You betrayed me, you prick.
What do you want?
I said I was sorry!
And seeing how I saved
your life and all...
I'm not really a traitor.
I thought you were
a businessman.
What happened to hitmen
being nothing but tools?
Well, yeah.
But I think men should
take care of their tools.
Especially when those tools
happen to be one of a kind.
Look who's dyin' now.
Think I promised to
kill you, too, traitor.
Like I said,
I didn't betray you.
I was planning
to double-cross Lau
and take his money
from the beginning.
But if I'd let you in on the
plan, he'd've caught on.
We both know you're
a terrible actor.
So give me a cut.
How's 20 percent?
That's kinda low.
Thirty sounds--
Zero point one five two.
That's even less.
It sounds like a
terrible batting average.
You know, there's a chance
that the next one
will actually hit you.
[sighs]
[FEILANG whistling]
[whistling]
[FEILANG]
Hey there, Mao.
Take a look at the fancy
watch this guy had.
Why the hell're you still alive?
[FEILANG]
Why?
Well, mostly because
you screwed up.
[FEILANG]
The guy who bought the bodies
realized I was still alive.
So, he treated my wounds.
And then he sold me
to an old sicko
who liked to torture kids.
I thought I knew what hell
was like before, but no.
Couldn't tell ya how many times
I wished you'd finished me off.
So you came here to take
revenge, is that right?
No. I came here
to take you back.
Let's work together, Mao.
We'll tour the world.
Make our fortune.
Try and figure out how
to enjoy our lives.
Just like we promised.
We're done.
And why is that?
Is it because of how I
stabbed you in the back?
[LIN]
That isn't why.
[FEILANG] We'll be rich
beyond our wildest dreams.
Poor as we were
growing up, we deserve it.
[LIN]
I don't care about money now.
[FEILANG]
Then what?
Why won't you work with me?
Because. I never want
to leave Fukuoka.
[FEILANG]
Uh--
I made friends in this
city. I found a home.
And I'm not about
to give that up.
In that case, I guess...
...I'll just destroy them.
This damn city. And every
last friend you have.
[LIN] So, the next
episode's the last one.
[BANBA] Yeah, and it's
the best one yet!
It's about me gettin'
scouted by the Hawks.
[LIN]
The hell it is!
[ENOKIDA] New series:
Hakata Enokida Hackers!
[BANBA]
No one would watch that!
[ENOKIDA]
You don't know!
[MARTÍNEZ]
What's goin' on?
[JIRO]
Banba got scouted.
[GENZOU]
What's wrong with my team?
--[YAMATO] Where are you going?
--[LIN] Shut up, you guys!
[BANBA] See ya, folks!
We'll be waitin' in Hakata!