Let's work together, Mao.
We're done.
And why is that?
Is it because of how I
stabbed you in the back?
[LIN]
That isn't why.
[FEILANG] Then what?
Why won't you work with me?
We'll be rich beyond
our wildest dreams.
[LIN]
I don't care about money now.
Because... I never
want to leave Fukuoka.
[FEILANG]
Uh--
I made friends in this
city. I found a home.
And I'm not about
to give that up.
In that case, I guess...
I'll just destroy them.
This damn city.
And every last friend
that you've made in it.
[LIN] Take that back.
Or I will kill you.
Here and now.
If that's how you want it,
then come at me.
You know I don't want this.
What's a hitman that's lost
his taste for killing?
Nothing but a coward,
if you ask me.
I think I'll help you remember
what you used to be.
The old you must be
somewhere in there.
Looks like you missed your mark.
No. I hit it.
[LIN grunts]
[FEILANG]
You can't escape from me, Mao.
[LIN panting]
Damn it all.
[sighs] He's still the
only one I can turn to.
[music plays]
[BANBA]
Good afternoon, Lin. What's up?
Ya know what, I think I see ya.
I'm gonna hang up now.
Banba. How did you--?
Enokida told me you
might be trouble.
Specifically, he said you ran
toward it like a dumbass.
I told him not to do that.
[BANBA]
And I found you
thanks to this little guy.
Guess who put it there.
As if there's information
that I can't find out.
Well, what a sneaky little shit.
[BANBA]
Anyway, let's go home.
Should I carry you?
I can walk just fine.
Yeah. You're as
stubborn as ever.
--C'mon, we've done it bef--
--[bang]
[gasps]
Banba!
[FEILANG] That's funny, I was
tryin' to shoot him in the leg.
But, then again I was
never much of a marksman.
[LIN]
Feilang, you bastard!
Like I said,
you can't escape me.
So this guy. What's he to you?
Don't tell me he's
one of those "friends"
that made you reject my offer.
[LIN]
No, don't!
Hey. Bring him with us.
Where the hell
are you taking him?
[FEILANG] Don't you worry.
We're taking you, too.
[ENOKIDA]
Hey, old man.
Hey, Enokida.
Seems like it's a bit early
for you to be out.
I suppose.
Hello, boys.
Good evening!
What's up.
How's it going?
Doubt you all came at
the same time by chance.
I take it you punks
are plotting something.
[ENOKIDA] Yeah, I think
you could say that.
We were hoping that you
might join us, Genzou.
Actually,
we want the hitman
Jiji to join us.
[gasps] Now that's a name I
haven't heard in a long time.
[grunts]
[LIN]
Damn it.
[gasps] Banba.
Hey. Wake up!
[BANBA groans]
I'm up. No need to yell.
[sighs]
Good. I kinda thought
you were dead.
Yeah, if they'd left me
there, I think I would be.
But for some reason,
they patched me up instead.
[LIN] My neck and ankle
should be killing me
but they're not. Think they
must've drugged, me.
[BANBA] Guess that means
they wanna keep us alive,
at least for now.
Well. Aren't'cha gonna ask?
Why? Do you want me to?
If you don't want to,
that's fine by me.
Nah, I was just kiddin'.
I'm dyin' to hear this!
Hurry up and tell. I'll
give ya this in exchange.
A piece of candy.
Yeah. All right.
So, the hitman that
shot me. You know him?
That's Feilang.
We were brought up in the
same training facility.
He was my best and
only friend there--
supposed to be my partner.
He was the only
person I could trust.
So when he literally
stabbed me in the back,
you could say it gave me
some serious trust issues
I haven't worked out.
I see. So that's
why you ran off?
Yeah. I bet that seems stupid.
Nah, it doesnt.
I've been betrayed by
someone I trusted, too.
I get it. It's smart to be wary.
It is. But sometimes...
...I meet people that
I want to trust.
And when that happens,
I take a chance.
Keeps things exciting.
I just couldn't take that again.
It hurts bad.
Turns men into wounded animals.
But someday, you
will trust again.
I mean, if everyone who screwed
up got cut from our team,
we couldn't play baseball.
Of course you looped
it to baseball.
So you're saying I'm a screw-up,
but you forgive me?
Yeah. You get it.
Point is, I trust you,
Lin. Completely.
[LIN] Moron. You just
wanna play baseball.
[BANBA chuckles]
That said, I'm starting
to see why you like it.
It's fun.
Told you.
This is it. Operation crybaby.
There is no better weapon
than a little girl's tears.
Try not to get upset
for real though.
You ready?
I can do this.
[JIRO]
Then let's go.
[gasps]
[LIN]
Well, for now,
we need to find a way
to get outta here.
Hey, Banba, are you listening?
Yeah. I hear you.
Well, that's reassuring.
Care to help?
From the look of things,
they've taken us into
the Kakyu headquarters.
What is this place?
It looks more like
a cage than a cell.
[LIN]
It's an execution room.
Seriously?
[LIN]
I've heard rumors about it.
Chairman Wang
originally built it
to house a tiger he bought.
But then, after the tiger died,
it became the place
where he would
take people he planned to kill.
Yeah. Looks like a tiger cage.
[door rattles]
[BANBA] Aw, someone put
their evil pants on today.
Feilang. What do you
plan to do with us?
Mao. They helped me
go through your phone.
And we were listening to your
whole conversation in there.
Are you seriously
on a baseball team?
You're a paid killer.
It helps me to work off
all the stress from my job.
Wouldn't wanna end up
all cranky like you.
Huh. Yeah. I guess I should
work off some stress, too.
[BOTH gasp]
The hell are those for?
Kinda slow on the uptake, Mao.
We've done this before.
Do you mean...?
You and your friend
will fight to the death.
Whichever one of you
survives can go free.
Now go and pick your weapons.
Banba.
[gasps]
[LIN] If he wanted to kill me,
that's not what he would choose.
I understand, Banba.
[LIN gasps]
I warned them that you
both would probably
try and pull a fast one
and pretend to fight.
I've known you for
five years, after all.
If you and your friend
continue refusing to fight.
Then I'll kidnap every person
on your baseball team,
one by one, and make
them do the same thing.
Until you finally grow
a pair and kill one.
Either you kill
one of your friends,
or I'll kill 'em all.
Starting with this one.
No! I'm the one
you're after, right?
Then shoot me!
Lin. It'll be okay.
[LIN] That's the sign
for a hit and run.
Just sprint on the
pitch and have faith.
'Cause the rest'll be in
the hands of your teammate.
[LIN] All right, Banba.
You'd better hit it.
I'm putting my faith in you.
[screams]
[LIN]
Gotcha.
[grunts]
And now for the heart.
[groans]
[BANBA]
Lin!
[JIRO]
Sorry, sir, but she really
needs to use your bathroom.
I gotta go, mister, please!
Just get outta here.
This establishment isn't
open to the public.
But I can't hold it!
I'm about to have an accident!
Yeah, so what?
You can go piss in your
pants for all I care!
Say what?
Look here.
There's no decent reason
for you to tell her
to embarrass herself like that,
and you sure as hell
better not be getting
off on picturing it!
Uh...
Just let the little girl
use the bathroom!
Hell hath no fury like
a strong gay man!
[sighs]
[HENCHMAN 12B]
Hey, hurry up in there!
I'm hurrying. Don't
rush me, mister.
[JIRO] The world's cutest spy
has entered the complex.
[ENOKIDA] Roger that. We can
take it from here, Jiro.
All set. Dr. Saeki?
[DR. SAEKI] After remotely
controlling robotic arms
to do surgery,
something like this should
be a piece of cake.
[ENOKIDA] How's it goin'
on your end, Jiji?
Ya get a connection yet?
I think so.
Hey! Banba. Do you read me?
[BANBA]
Yeah. I hear you.
We're in business.
We've managed to track ya
to the building you're in.
It's the Kakyu association's HQ.
From the look of things,
they've taken us into
the Kakyu headquarters.
[GENZOU] We're gonna need
some help to pinpoint
your exact location.
Tell us what you see.
[BANBA]
What is this place?
It looks more like
a cage than a cell.
[LIN]
It's an execution room.
--[gasps]
--[BANBA] Seriously?
I think I know where they are.
[ENOKIDA]
Our spies mentioned the place.
It was the chairman's
private execution chamber.
He used to keep
a tiger in there.
Yeah. Looks like a tiger cage.
Sounds like you were right.
Hey, Dr. Saeki.
You're gonna need to take
a hard right in 30 meters,
and then you can go
straight for 20.
Understood.
[GENZOU]
I'm in position.
Count down when you're ready.
And now for the heart.
[groans]
We gotta move!
Lin!
Three!
Two!
[BOTH]
One!
[LIN]
Feilang's gone.
Ah--
You can't kill him.
I won't let you.
He has to survive.
He's the only one
who can save Lee.
[LIN growls]
[gunfire]
[LIN] Why is the old man
dressed like that?
[BANBA]
Ah, the infamous Jiji returns.
Yeah, for a one night
only comeback show.
Here.
I need a smaller act like
the Niwaka Samurai to open.
Yeah, I can make ya
look impressive.
I mean, I am wounded.
Plucky twerp.
--[HENCHMAN 12C] This way!
--[HENCHMAN 12D] Hurry!
[HENCHMAN 12E]
Don't let them leave alive!
Uh--
[yells]
[HENCHMEN yelling]
[laughing]
[GENZOU laughing]
The old man's still got it.
[LIN]
Banba.
I'm going after Feilang.
You think that's a good idea?
You could let me
take care of it.
Thanks, but... You've
helped me enough.
I have to do this myself.
All right then.
Take care of yourself.
Yeah. See ya.
All right. I've got
some catchin' up to do.
[ENOKIDA] Now that I've got
access to their computers,
I can figure out where
the executives are hiding.
Keep me safe, okay?
I'm a very delicate boy.
Yeah, yeah.
I was hopin' I'd get
to see some action.
[footsteps]
What the hell are you
doing down here?
Ah, yes. That is the question.
[crashing, yelling]
Try and keep it down
out there, Maru.
Well, that ended quickly.
There were lots of 'em,
but they were all pushovers.
[SARUWATARI]
What happened here?
Saru. Come by to
complicate things?
Nah, you're not the
person I came here for.
Know where the
redheaded hitman is?
Ugh. Forget it.
I'll find him myself.
If you're planning to kill him,
I can't let you pass.
My friend Lin is
in the middle of
settling his own score with him.
Oh, yeah? So you're
gonna get in my way?
If you insist on killing him,
first, you'll have
to get through me.
That's how it is.
Normally, I'd leap at the
chance to beat your ass!
But if you think you can
take me right now,
you must not think much of me.
[sighs]
[SARUWATARI]
I'll leave you be for now.
But this isn't the end of it.
Once you're done healing up,
you owe me a fight.
That was a good throw.
Someones been hitting
the pitching cage.
Hell yeah, I have.
I'll strike you out in
three pitches next game.
Hey, welcome back.
Did ya kill the redhead?
No, but... I think I'm over it.
Huh? So then...?
Yeah. Let's head home to Kokura.
[LIN panting]
[LIN]
The anesthetic's wearing off.
And I feel like I
haven't slept in a week.
[FEILANG whistling]
[whistling continues]
Dunno how you feel,
but my guts're killin' me.
That was an impressive shot,
considering what all
was goin' on back there.
You were always the better shot
back at the factory, too.
Yeah, but you were
always better than me
when it came to
hand to-hand combat.
English as well.
Heh. And then you'd beat me
when it came to Japanese.
Ya see? I meant it when I told
ya we'd make a great team.
It's not too late either.
You and me? Workin' together?
We'd have nothing
to fear in the world.
Sorry, but there's
not a chance in hell.
So you really like
this city that much.
[LIN] Yeah. I wanna live
my whole life here.
I'll play ball, n' eat
ramen for breakfast,
and talk about idiotic things
with a whole bunch of idiots.
And, well... if you really
want to destroy that,
then I'll...
--We both know you can't ki--
--[LIN] I will kill you.
[gasps]
[LIN] Yeah. I'm not
that child anymore.
[grunts]
It's no use, the knife's
too far to reach.
You don't know the state
of the field, but I do.
This time, I'll make sure
you don't come back.
Goodbye, Fei.
[FEILANG sputters]
Ya know, you've always
had what I couldn't.
What I could never
quite find for myself.
I was always jealous,
Mao. I wanted...
Damn, did they make a mess.
Don't they know that I have
to clean up after them?
[OFFICER 12A]
Sir, where do you want unit 2?
[SHIGEMATSU] Cancel it.
These guys are all very dead.
Hey there. How was your night?
Yeah.
How was your night?
[sighs]
Great, how was yours?
[bang]
[UMPIRE]
Strike!
Nice! One more and he's out!
Yeah. I realize that, Naoya.
Make sure ya catch it.
No prob.
Two outs in the bottom of
the ninth with bases loaded.
It's okay to bunt, Banba!
You only need to get a run!
True.
But if I know Banba,
he's gonna go for the win.
[JIRO]
I think so, too.
After all, his ex is watching.
Come on! Finish him off, Saru!
Banba, the trick is to swing
the bat at the ball!
Hey, Banba!
Get a hit or you can't have any
spicy pollock roe this week!
You hear that, Sarucchi?
Don't get between a man
and his soul food.
Ha! I said I'd strike
you out in three pitches.
Just throw me my
Grand Slam, 'kay?