[footsteps]
[SARUWATARI] Are you the
so-called Niwaka Samurai?
Yeah, that'd be me.
[SARUWATARI]
Shorter than I thought you'd be.
Kinda girly.
I was told that I'd be
assigned a target here.
Who am I killing?
[SARUWATARI]
Try me.
[gasps]
[SARUWATARI]
If you manage to defeat me,
then you'll be paid
what we agreed.
Not bad!
[phone vibrating]
[LIN] Hey, old man.
Banba's passed out again.
Says he's got an
early start tomorrow.
Makes sense.
They're gonna have
the big Oiyama race.
[LIN]
This about a job?
If you want, I can
handle it for you.
[GENZOU] Nah, I could only put
Banba himself on this one.
And why is that?
[GENZOU] The client asked for
the Niwaka Samurai specifically.
Even said he'd pay
twice the normal fee.
Huh.
Well, guess we'll just
have to turn them down.
[LIN]
Oh. Banba just got up.
He's in the bathroom.
Oh? Ask him then.
[LIN] Hey, Banba.
Feel up to a job tonight?
[LIN]
'Kay. He says he'll do it.
He wants me to get the
time and place for him.
[panting]
[LIN]
Who the hell is this guy?
Why did I take this stupid job?
[SARUWATARI] Oh, come on.
Is this all you've got?
You'd better not be another
easy kill. Fight damn it!
[BANBA groans]
[BANBA yawns]
Lin already took off?
Eh, he is a full-grown man.
I bet he's out havin'
fun somewhere.
[LIN grunting]
[SARUWATARI] What's the
matter, hitman killer?
I thought you were
s'posed to be tough!
[yelps]
Screw it, this thing's too slow!
[SARUWATARI]
Ah...
[car engine revs]
[SARUWATARI]
What the...?
[LIN]
What?
Hey! Who the hell--?
[LIN screams]
[SARUWATARI]
Huh? Hey! You bastards!
What the...?
Shit! Shit! Shit!
[YAMA] That went pretty
smooth. He's sound asleep.
We just caught the
Niwaka Samurai, Dude!
Yeah.
That stupid-looking ninja guy
made a pretty good diversion.
We just made 100,000,000 yen!
[LIN]
Shit. I'm the damsel yet again.
Banba's gonna give me the
longest lecture of my life.
Look at that. They bit!
Say what?
[MARTÍNEZ] I just got
my first online client!
Remember how I made a profile
on that shady jobs website?
Oh. Good for you.
So what do they need?
Let's see.
"We need you to
torture a tough guy
to get information out of him.
We beat his brains out
and he won't even scream.
Please get back to us ASAP."
Hey. Web is good for
more than cat pics.
"Send me a photo and
any details you have
on the target, and I'll
give you a quote." And sent.
[SARUWATARI]
This is the van all right.
How'd you find it?
I got an anonymous hacker
to track its path
from the garage with security
and traffic cameras
Had to get it fast,
so the guy gouged me.
Cash in the bank.
Ugh.
Uh-- Wait. Shouldn't
we plan this?
[SARUWATARI grunts]
You've got some balls
to steal my mark
from right in front of me.
We're sorry! It was stupid!
We only tried it 'cause
we lost our jobs!
We're flat broke, man!
Like I care.
[BOTH gasp]
[SARUWATARI]
Where's the Niwaka Samurai?
Huh?
[SARUWATARI] Damn it all.
What the hell have you done?
You stupid bastards.
That kill was
supposed to be mine!
Wait, it's not
what it looks like.
That guy was a fake.
The Niwaka Samurai's alive!
Huh?
That's a fake?
How would you know?
Yeah, listen.
I met a guy at a bar who fought
the real Niwaka Samurai.
He lost an eye to him.
This one didn't
look anything like
how the guy had described him.
He was taller. Short brown hair.
This guy even admitted
he was just a fake.
So we tried to torture
him so he'd tell us
where the real one was, but...
He died before we got
another word out of him.
But it wasn't
our fault, I swear!
We beat on him,
but he wouldn't break,
so we called in a pro.
But he was, like,
the worst torturer ever!
A damn fake?
Huh?
[SARUWATARI]
The hell! He's screwing with me!
That bastard! He's too
scared to fight me himself!
[SARUWATARI pants]
[NAOYA]
Calm down, Sarucchi.
If this guy knew the real one,
then, hey. Maybe we
can use this as bait.
[GENZOU panting]
There you are. Banba!
[BANBA]
Hey, boss. Somethin' wrong?
You look stressed.
[GENZOU]
Damn straight I am, come here.
I thought something was off.
It's not like you to take
a job before the Oiyama,
not even for double.
But who'd've thought that Lin
would go in your place?
[gasps]
"If you want to save him,
then come to this
location by 4:30."
[gasps]
Although, by the look of him,
it might already be too late.
[BANBA]
You're right, but I'm going.
Huh?
Whether they've killed him
or not, it doesn't matter.
Can't just leave
him alone there.
Thought's too sad.
Dead or alive,
I'm bringing him back.
[MAN 6D] Banba! We're just
about to start, c'mon.
[BANBA sighs] Sorry, but
I'm needed somewhere else.
[MAN 6D]
Huh? You're kidding.
Banba, wait. Come back!
[SARUWATARI sighs] First one
I met looked like a woman.
And now you show up
dressed like this.
Are you the real
Niwaka Samurai, or not?
I'm him. Where's the
man from the text?
[NAOYA]
Yes, Lee? As we promised.
The Niwaka Samurai
will soon be dead.
Uh. Excuse me?
[SARUWATARI]
Sorry, he's already dead.
Though I'm not
the one who did it.
[BANBA sighs]
Such a pretty face.
Almost like a mortician
already worked on him.
[SARUWATARI]
Hey.
Draw and come at me.
[BANBA]
The big race is about to start.
I don't have time
to play with you.
[SARUWATARI]
Forget about the festival.
If you really wanna see it, then
you'll have to kill me first.
[sighs]
[LEE]
Excellent work.
But your job is finished now.
We'll be taking the
Niwaka Samurai with us.
[SARUWATARI]
Wait, you're the guy from Kakyu?
What kinda joke is this?
Restrain him.
What's the big idea?
You hired me, so just
let me finish him!
The circumstances have changed.
Our chairman decided he'd
like to do the deed himself.
Easier for us, right?
Sorry, Sarucchi!
[SARUWATARI] To hell with that!
He's mine. I'll kill him!
Just let it go, Sarucchi.
You'll receive the
amount we agreed upon
in full, don't worry.
Pleasure doing business.
Hey! Come back here!
I told you, he's mine!
There's nothing we
can do. Let it go.
You told those pricks
where we were.
Double-crossing bastard.
I oughtta kill you.
If that'll make you feel
better, then go for it.
Yes, sir.
We've captured
the Niwaka Samurai.
Well done.
See that the execution
chamber is ready.
I'm on my way.
What's that? You're leaving now?
And after I've waited
so long. You cruel man.
[WANG] Don't worry. I'll
satisfy you before I leave.
[SAYURI]
I know you will.
[SARUWATARI]
Shit, shit, shit!
[NAOYA]
Sarucchi.
Huh?!
Check it out.
I put a tracker on the Kakyu
association guy's car.
Some things matter more
than 100,000,000 yen.
Especially for a guy
like you, right?
[laughs] You should've
told me sooner!
I knew you were a good partner!
Hey. How are you feelin'?
About how I imagine
a corpse would.
This suitcase reeks
of death, by the way.
Yeah, no helpin' that.
It's the same case I brought
your body double in.
Sure was surprised
you showed up.
I mean, one minute
those lowlife assholes
were threatening me with the
torture sesh of a lifetime.
And the next, I see
my old baseball pal.
[MARTÍNEZ] I was just
as shocked as you were.
There I was, lookin' forward
to some honest work,
when the client sent
me your picture.
We all scrambled to
come up with a plan.
N' we landed on
faking your death.
Wasn't easy to find a body
like yours so quickly.
I'll take credit for that part.
Think I must've set some
records fixing up the face.
The hair wasn't all that hard.
At least not for an expert
stylist such as yours truly.
Okay, I'm grateful, guys.
Now let up on me, will ya?
Can I just say one thing?
You really shouldn't pretend
to be the Niwaka Samurai.
[sighs] I know, sorry.
Hey. It's okay to just be you.
I mean it.
That's what Jiro told
me a long time ago.
Ah, shut your trap.
I get lectured plenty
without you joinin' in.
Ya plucky brat.
Well, anyway.
If you guys don't mind,
I'm gonna hit the can.
That punk.
Always with the tough façade.
[LIN] I bet the festival's
started by now.
[LIN]
Hey old man. Listen.
[GENZOU]
Lin! We thought you were dead!
Huh?
Damn it, Banba. You moron!
Hey. What time is it?
Shut up.
[groans] Damn, this sucks.
I'm gonna miss the
race for sure now.
[THUG 6B groans]
[THUG 6C]
We need backup!
[THUGS groaning]
Whew! Thanks a bunch.
But, why would you rescue me?
[SARUWATARI]
I can't kill you if you're dead.
[THUG 6F whimpers]
[screams]
Worst throw I've seen in years.
Throw that with
your eyes closed?
[SARUWATARI]
Shut up!
Just need time
to warm up, okay?
[BANBA, SARUWATARI]
Huh?
[SARUWATARI]
Oh, Shit.
[BANBA]
That's our cue to run.
The ninja betrayed us.
Capture if possible,
but if not, then kill them.
'Scuse me. Bad news.
The chairman's been killed.
Say what? You mean Longfang?
Forget about those two.
Let's go.
[SARUWATARI] Huh? They gave up
just like that? Well then.
We can pick this up
where we left off.
To be honest, I'd like
to take a raincheck.
What's your next week look
like? I'm thinkin' Thursday.
[SARUWATARI]
What's the problem?
Scared I'll kick your ass?
"Scared," huh?
Not quite the word I would use.
[MEN]
Oisa ! Oisa ! Oisa !
[BANBA yells]
[door opens]
I wish you'd explained more
when you invited me up here.
You got my hopes up.
So sorry, Naoya.
Oh. Thanks for providing
that distraction, by the way.
How did you do it?
I'd heard that every
woman brought to his bed
is subjected to a
full-body cavity search.
You heard right. That said,
no one thought to check for
the poison I put under these.
You're a scary woman, Sayuri.
So. I'm quite curious.
Who is it that's crazy
enough to put out a hit
on the Kakyu Association's head?
Oh, he's a madman.
Huh. You're actually not bad.
Neither are you.
Yes! Nailed it.
Huh?
[SARUWATARI]
The hell--?
[SARUWATARI yelps]
That was a close one.
Here. I'll pull you back up.
Why the hell would you help me?
I still owe you from before.
[SARUWATARI]
Look, I didn't free you
out of the kindness of my heart.
Maybe not.
But if I let you fall,
you'll ruin the festivities.
Climb up. We'll
call this a draw.
Let those people have their fun.
[SARUWATARI grumbles]
[sighs]
[ABE, YAMA groan]
Think that oughtta do it.
It's a beating for
a beating, isn't it?
You got it.
We avengers only deal out
what was dealt to our client.
Although...
It's always possible
to overdo it by mistake.
Why, I've even heard
of hitmen killing
the wrong person just because
he had a similar name.
[MEN] Oisa ! Oisa ! Oisa !
Oisa ! Oisa ! Oisa !
[NAOYA]
Hey! That you, Sarucchi?
I'm glad to hear
you're alive, bud.
[SARUWATARI]
Gee, thanks.
Glad to know you believe in me.
[NAOYA]
So what happened?
You beat the Niwaka Samurai?
[SARUWATARI]
Nope. It was just a draw.
[NAOYA]
Huh? How'd that happen?
Hey, Naoya. I gotta say.
This city's warmin' up on me.
[BANBA singing in Japanese]
[LIN]
Banba!
[BANBA]
Hm?
Uh, Hey, Lin. You all right?
[LIN] That's supposed
to be my line.
Why didn't you answer
your damn phone?
Ah. I put it on silent
and forgot about it.
Huh? How did that
thing get on there?
It took you this long to notice?
[sighs]
[LIN] So, I heard that
you ran out after me,
thinking I had been killed.
[BANBA]
That's a lie. I mostly walked.
[LIN] Can't believe you thought
I'd get done in that easily.
You always underestimate me.
[BANBA]
I didn't underestimate you.
I was just worried is all.
Uh--
I'm sorry about the false alarm.
And for pretending to
be the Niwaka Samurai.
Eh. All's well that
ends well, I say.
Although...
[gasps]
The Yamakasa is all
over now! Sad day.
Why'd I have to miss the Oiyama?
I was looking forward
to it all year.
Oh, you'll be fine.
There's always next year.
That is so not the point, Lin.
This year's Oiyama only
happens this year.
Today was s'posed
to be my reward
for all this year's hard woork.
Uh, okay. Let's go.
We can grab some ramen
on the way home.
I'll even buy this time.
[BANBA]
With spicy pollock roe?
[LIN]
Not that again.
[sighs]
Good work.
That pitcher's got
such lousy aim
that it's hard to hit on him.
Yeah. That is true.
Damn. Their manager's a hottie!
Whoa! She really is.
Hold on. I know her somehow.
Didn't she and Banba used to--
[gasps]
[MEN groaning]
[BANBA]
Agh. Son of a--
Hey, what's with these pitches?
You almost hit me right
in the head that time!
Screw you! Just
square up and swing.
You little...
Not good.
[MEN chattering]
[BANBA]
You almost hit me!
At least pull your cap up!
He's as insane as ever, I see.
Did you throw that
with your eyes closed?
Shut up! I just need time
to warm up, damn it!
[gasps]
[BANBA, SARUWATARI yell]
[SAEKI] There's something
I'd like you to look into.
[ENOKIDA]
Counter Cybercrime Unit?
[JIRO]
Ew, that's too raw.
[BANBA]
Hey, what the hell?
[ENOKIDA] If I need help,
I'll contact you.
[BANBA]
They sure did a number on ya.
[ENOKIDA]
I was killed.