[RINO]
Welcome back to class.
Okay, now that your second
semester has officially begun,
it's time to present
your summer research projects.
Yayoi, you're up first.
I was fortunate enough to be
tutored by a family friend
who's a cultural expert.
By using traditional
Japanese crafting techniques,
I created a Disfia Foreigner
in the wooden mosaic style.
[RINO]
Wow.
Amazing!
That looks like a
professional piece of art.
Is there some kind of problem?
It's fine.
Next is Karin and Karen.
Come on down you two.
I heard you worked
on a project together.
So this is, um...
What am I looking at?
Please give us a minute.
It's supposed to be
a Tritomy-like
Foreigner robot model.
I'm drinking as fast as I can.
I apologize.
Clearly I was negligent
in supervising them.
How 'bout we move on?
Lion's up.
What did you bring?
Is this a bear carving?
That's right!
Daddy showed me how to carve
the wood myself with a knife.
[KAGURA] You managed to
make this with just a knife?
That's quite an amazing feat.
[BELLE screeches]
[YAYOI] Isn't that salmon
in its mouth a little too big?
It's actually a tuna.
[OTHERS]
A tuna?
Why a tuna?
Because it's my favorite fish!
Oh--I see.
All right. It's your
turn to present, Nina.
Uh, so... what's all this?
[NINA] I measured the pulses
of a Cepheid variable star,
and observed the distance
between astronomical objects
outside our galaxy, while noting
the expansion of our universe.
Good job.
Who can follow this?
--[MAHIRO panting]
--[RINO] Let's see. Next is--
I don't think she can wait.
It looks like she
can't contain herself.
[MAHIRO chuckles]
[KAGURA, RINO]
This can't be good.
[RINO] Against my
better judgment, I'll ask.
What's this?
All right! It's my latest model
of a Powered Suit
that allows a normal human
to safely enter a Paradox Zone!
With my perfected suits,
non-Logicalists will be able to
move freely into
these dangerous areas,
in order to save injured people
or do whatever else
they'd like to in that space!
And hopefully someday,
we humans will be able to
use these suits to
visit other worlds!
It's cardboard.
Since this is the prototype,
I kinda had to use
what I could get my hands on.
If you're ready,
let's see it in action.
No! We'll do that later!
--[MAHIRO whines]
--[RINO sighs]
Wh-Why don't you
want me to try it out?
I almost forgot!
There's new info
about the school festival.
And your class still needs
to nominate a project leader.
I'm sorry, I didn't realize
we needed a leader.
Yes, you all need to pick
a student representative
to be in charge
of your class project.
And I'm sure you wouldn't mind
if we left all the details
to you, Yayoi.
Indeed.
Now the principal has
asked to meet with us,
so we'll need to talk to you
about this sometime later.
Come see us in the staff room
once you've decided on things.
[KAGURA, RINO]
Later!
Uh, did they run away from me?
They're leaving
everything up to us.
Well yeah, we are
first-year class S, after all.
[YAYOI]
In any case.
I will take over now,
and we'll soon resolve
the matter of project leader.
[school bell chimes]
There's a school announcement?
Yuko wouldn't answer
my calls or text messages.
I need to know, where was she
during summer break?
[gasps]
At home, at home, at home.
A heart mark?!
What could that
possibly symbolize?
Doesn't say.
[door opens]
Just so you know,
the camera is rolling.
The broadcast has been live
for a few minutes.
[MIZUKI]
What?!
[MIZUKI gasps]
Okay, little girls.
Let's keep this a secret
just between us.
[MIZUKI gasps]
Yuko!
I can explain!
--[slap]
--[MIZUKI gasps]
This is an
interesting announcement.
[sighs] I apologize for exposing
you to such an unsightly scene.
Let's start over, shall we?
Pirari Academy's first
school festival is coming.
Using our co-existence with
Foreigners as the theme,
we'd like for each class,
committee, and club
to come up with an activity.
And in order to increase morale
across the student body,
we here at student council
will be running a popularity
contest between each event.
If we all aim for first place,
then there's no way
this won't be the
best school festival possible.
That's it.
This student council
message is over now.
Yuko, please listen to me.
What you saw--
--[slap]
--[MIZUKI yelps]
A popularity contest, huh?
I wonder if they're
gonna give us a prize
for winning first place.
I hope it's something awesome
like an all-you-can-eat buffet.
Let's not get
too ahead of ourselves.
First we need to decide
on what we should do.
All right.
Does anyone have a good idea?
What kind of events
do people normally throw
at school festivals?
I think we should just go with
the standard maid cafe.
[ALL]
Welcome to our cafe.
Care for some tea?
That'd be so cute!
[KAREN]
Or maybe a heart-pounding,
blood-curdling haunted house?
--[ALL groaning, mumbling]
--[YAYOI] Gimme your brains!
I wanna be a zombie!
Me too!
I think it'd be super exciting
for everyone involved.
I say no.
Why you don't you
like that idea?
Don't tell me that you're
afraid of supernatural beings.
I can see that.
No. I'm not scared
of the undead.
[LION]
It's okay.
Ghosts are nothing
to be scared of.
[BELLE whimpers]
All right,
that's enough, ladies.
Doesn't matter if ghosts are
real or not, the idea's out.
[LION, BELLE, KAREN]
Huh?
[NINA sighs]
Let's try focusing on
the school festival's theme.
How can we best showcase our
coexistence with the Foreigners?
Understand?
We have to do something
way more academic
if we want to win this contest.
Oh, I get it!
Now, I wonder what kinda
neat thing we could do.
[KAGURA]
Regarding Lion,
I'll be conducting
extracurricular lessons with her
this semester on how to resolve
her unstable Trance situation.
The fluctuating light that
scatters across will surely...
...appear as fleeting
as ever before.
You understand, right?
Because you should.
You must remember to always
keep a vigilant eye on her.
[KAGURA]
I will.
[YAYOI]
Okay!
Does anyone else have an idea?
[MAHIRO]
Me!
Wouldn't it be really cool
for our class to sing a song?
[OTHERS]
A song?
I couldn't stop thinking
about it during our break.
Remember that song Lion
sang to us under the stars?
She told us it's from Monolium.
[LION] Really?
You wanna sing that song?
It could teach us something
special about Foreigner culture.
And it fits perfectly
with the festival's theme!
Don't you girls agree?
[LION gasps]
Certainly.
And I believe that it's a
wonderful and very unique idea.
But unless I'm mistaken here,
we only have the one
short Foreigner song
that Lion's mother taught her.
Do you know any others?
Can we really convey anything
with just one song?
Yeah, you've got a point.
Well, now perhaps we take the
feelings put into Lion's song,
and come up with another way
to communicate that message
to the festival goers.
We can turn the song
into part of a story!
I'm not quite sure I understand.
Just how do you
plan on doing that?
We'll put on a performance!
A musical play!
[OTHERS]
A musical play?
[STUDENTS chattering]
This sounds like it'll be fun!
What will the story be about?
Uh-uhh.
[MAHIRO]
Lion, sing the song
so everyone else can hear
what we're talking about.
Hm?
Just wait, this thing's
got a karaoke mode too.
[LION] Wow! Look at the way
its face lights up!
[YUKO] Oh! My tea stem
is floating upright.
Nice!
That means good fortune.
Maybe. But I don't forgive you
for that invasion of privacy.
Uh, well, anyway,
the only group that hasn't
submitted their
festival paperwork yet
is Miss Kagura's
first-year class S.
You know what kind
of students they are.
I'm sure they're all just
exploding with--
We might be waiting
a while longer.
Of course.
[RINO] Hm? A musical
using a Foreigner song.
Wow, that's such an
original idea.
Okay. So who's going to be
writing the script?
Since I came up with it,
I'll be the writer.
What kind of story will it be?
[MAHIRO] I haven't really
worked that out yet.
Tell me that you're joking!
I assume that Ya--
Oh, what's this?
The form says
the project leader is Mahiro?
Huh? Well, that's
clearly a mistake.
Our class representative will--
It's right.
Mahiro's in charge this time.
Wha...?
[YAYOI, MAHIRO]
Please excuse us.
[door opens]
[sighs] It's weird that
I'm the project leader now.
That's way too much
responsibility.
So, why didn't you want to be
the one in charge anyway?
I originally planned on
taking on the leadership role,
as I usually do.
But after hearing you speak,
I decided that you were the
perfect person for the job.
Mahiro.
Huh?
I felt that the person
leading our class project
should be the one who's always
been the most passionate
about Foreigners
and their culture.
[LION humming]
[MAHIRO yells]
[MAHIRO]
This sucks!
Why can't I think of
anything good to write?
[LION] It sounds like she's
taking this play very seriously.
[MAHIRO groans]
[yells]
[MAHIRO] Whoever said the god
of playwrights would visit me
is a dirty liar!
[LION, BELLE snoring]
[BOTH sigh]
[MAHIRO snores]
Did she really think we were
dumb enough to fall for that?
So weird.
She even went through the
trouble of painting eyes on.
I'm kinda impressed though
That's the only thing
you have to say?
If she hadn't stayed up
all night to build that thing,
she'd be awake now.
[MAHIRO snores]
Hello! I'm Mahiro!
[ROBO-GIRL]
Robo-Girl.
And the two of us
together make--
[ROBO-GIRL]
Robo-Girl.
--[CROWD laughs]
--Is that so?
That's quite the schtick
you've got going on there.
Robo-Girl here is visiting us
from the world Tritomy.
There anything you'd
like us to know about you?
[ROBO-GIRL]
Robo-Girl.
Jeez, is Robo-Girl the only
thing you know how to say?
[ROBO-GIRL]
Robo-Girl.
--[CROWD laughs]
--You sure are a stiff one.
Say, I wonder what kind
of people live on Tritomy.
I'd sure like to meet 'em.
[ROBO-GIRL]
Robo-Girl.
--[CROWD laughs]
--[MAHIRO] Come on!
Now you're starting to sound
like some kind of broken robot!
[ROBO-GIRL]
Robo-Girl.
I had that one--
[groans]
--[CROWD laughs, applauds]
--Even your body's stiff!
[ROBO-GIRL]
Robo-Girl.
[groans]
--[STUDENTS laughing]
--[YAYOI] Wake up, Mahiro!
The four of you who
possess multiple covenants
will be participating
in a mock battle today.
But I'm sleepy.
First things first,
you all should Trance now.
[YAYOI, LION, NINA]
Got it!
Here!
[YAYOI] This will be
our first battle, Nagi!
[NAGI] Do you really think
you can handle my power?
[MAHIRO]
Gate Access!
Tritomy!
C'mon, Dread!
Let's go in with a bang!
[DREAD]
Sounds good!
Go get 'em!
I just Tranced
with my new covenant!
Yay!
Let's begin the mock battle.
--[MAHIRO yawns]
--Yayoi and Mahiro.
--You're up first.
[BOTH]
Okay!
I would start running
if I were you.
'Cause this move
is my "wake up call"!
Come on, you know messy shots
like that will never hit me!
Hey, Nina! Time to play with me!
--[LION giggles]
--Okay. Lion and Nina are next.
Begin.
I'm comin' for you!
[LION grunts]
[giggles] I'm not gonna lose!
[LION yells]
[NINA] She's fast, but I'm
not going along with this game.
Trance Change!
[giggles]
[gasps]
If that's how you wanna play,
I'll join you!
Trance Change again!
Wow.
She's so good.
Calling to Waffle.
[LION groans]
[KAGURA] I'd hoped pairing you
with such a childish partner
would allow you
to retain control.
It seems I was mistaken.
Because your propensity to
empathize with the Foreigners
is too strong.
[sighs]
Miss Kagura.
What am I supposed to do?
You need to train
both your heart and body.
Let me think.
From now on you'll be
meeting with me regularly
for some intensive
one-on-one combat training.
But what kind of lessons
should I take to train my heart?
That's a good question.
[BELLE whines]
[BELLE squeaks]
[LION squeals]
[BELLE whines]
What was that?
[KAGURA] It seems as though
you're sensitive
to other people's
feelings as well.
Did that frighten you?
Well, uh... just a little bit.
[KAGURA]
Now look in the mirror.
Even with
a small threat like that,
your emotions start to run wild.
Disrupting your
Trance's balance.
Our training sessions
will not be limited
to just your combat skills.
We'll also focus
on your emotions.
Understand?
[LION]
Miss Kagura.
[LION] Can you tell me what it
means to be a strong Logicalist?
And how do you know
if you're good enough?
[KAGURA] There is a reason
you're asking me, right?
Um, well...
I know this girl
who's really strong,
but she has to
make herself even stronger!
Or more like,
she has to prove to people
that she's gotten stronger.
Does that make any sense?
Yeah...
I tried to come up with
a solution for her,
but I couldn't
think of any good ones...
You see,
I wanna help her.
There's gotta be something
I can do to cheer her on.
The best thing for you to do
is stay by her side.
[KAGURA]
Anyone would feel stupid
worrying about their own
problems when they look at you.
[gasps]
[whines]
[LION]
What's that supposed to mean?
I wish I knew how to
make it back into ALCA.
[MAHIRO yells, whines]
[MAHIRO] The god of playwrights
keeps refusing to visit me!
[MAHIRO groans]
Please, God!
Buddha!
I'll even take an angel
at this point!
[MAHIRO sighs]
I can't do this
without some divine help.
An angel.
That's it!
[MAHIRO]
Yeah.
I know what to write about now.
I've got it!
Ah, ha, ha! God has
finally spoken to me!
No, actually, it was more like
an angel and flower sprite!
[LION, BELLE snoring]
--[footsteps]
--[LION, BELLE snoring]
[YAYOI] What are you doing
sleeping in the dining hall?
I didn't wanna bother Mahiro
while she was busy trying to
write our class musical.
Well, this won't do at all.
Why don't you get off the floor
and come sleep in my room?
Huh?
You're so sweet.
But you didn't need to
go out of your way like that.
Once Mahiro starts
working on a new assignment,
she's oblivious to
everything else around her.
It's fine.
I was just trying to
give her some space.
[YAYOI] No matter what task
Mahiro decides to take on,
you can rest assured she's
putting all her energy into it.
Of course, she's failed
more times than not.
But then, she wouldn't
be Mahiro otherwise.
I always forget that
you've been friends with her
since you were little kids.
That's right.
And I swear, she hasn't
changed a bit since then.
[BOTH giggle]
[sighs]
It took me all night,
but I finally finished.
Lion? Can you read this for me?
Lion?
Wait a sec. Where is she?
[STUDENTS chattering]
[MAHIRO]
It took a lot of work, but--
I'm finally done
writing our class musical!
That's so awesome!
Thanks, Lion.
I think I'm really
on to something!
So, Mahiro.
Tell us what kind of story
you decided to write.
Well, in short,
it's kind of about friendship.
A Foreigner girl from
Monolium comes to Septpia
but ends up lost and alone
on a strange planet.
Then she meets a local girl
and they communicate
with each other through song!
[STUDENTS]
Wow!
That sounds like
a really good story.
Thank you.
And so, uh, I... I guess
I should announce the cast too.
There're two lead roles.
The girl from Septpia
will be played by Nina.
--[STUDENTS chatter]
--[NINA] But, but I've never...
And the Foreigner girl from
Monolium will be played by Lion.
What? Why me?
It makes sense
'cause it's your song!
Sure! Leave it to me!
[KAGURA] That was our
last visit to the beach.
[RINO] Please,
I don't wanna talk about it.
What? Are you sad?
Is it because nobody
even tried to talk to us?
I can't hear you,
I can't hear you. I can't...
--[RINO cries]
--Fine, I get it.
--I'll stop talking.
Oh, wait! It's almost autumn now
and that's the season of food--
Well don't start stuffing
your face until summer's over.
[KOZUE]
Autumn's coming.
The season of love.
Eh?
[KAGURA]
Vice Principal?
[RINO] You think you'll
meet a guy in autumn?
C'mon, the fall's
when people get dumped.
[KOZUE]
Look at that,
still holding on
to old traditions.
[RINO]
O-Old?
[KOZUE] Is there a better
season than autumn
to have a quiet encounter
with nature?
[PRINCIPAL] As the colors
of autumn deepen,
people begin to seek
the warmth of one another.
[KAGURA]
You too?
Wait, what does that even--
[RINO]
Autumn means Mr. Right.
Mr. Right means autumn!
[KOZUE, PRINCIPAL, RINO]
Let's all get out there and
find our man!
[KAGURA] Yeah, something's wrong
with the entire teaching staff.
[BELLE huffs]