[MIZUKI]
Sleeping like a baby.
[giggles]
It's about time
for her to wake up.
Today's career counseling day.
Good morning, honey.
Rise and shine.
[MIZUKI]
Great.
Yuko's in a good mood again.
She gets a gold star.
[MIZUKI humming]
[YUKO]
Goodness. Is that a bird?
[MIZUKI gasps]
Tweet! Tweet, tweet, tweet!
Tweet, tweet!
[YUKO]
How wonderful.
I'm so happy a birdie's
come to play with me!
[MIZUKI whining]
[MIZUKI] This is bad!
She's gonna see me!
Oh, my.
[phone ringing]
[YUKO]
Hi, Lion! How are you?
Hello?
I've really missed you!
You good?
[YUKO]
What was that?
Sorry, I can't hear you.
[LION]
How are you?
[YUKO]
Oh. I'm doing well. And you?
[LION]
I'm great!
I'll be back at
the dorms tomorrow.
Yeah? What a nice surprise.
Be careful on your way here.
She looks so cute
when she smiles.
[ladder clatters]
[MIZUKI gasps]
Oh, no!
[screams]
[TEACHER 7A]
Miss Morigaya.
[YUKO]
Coming.
Excuse me. [door closes]
[AOI]
Yuko? Hey. Yuko, you with us?
We're so sorry
for making you wait.
It's fine. Shall we
head into town now?
We can't go yet.
President's not here.
[YUKO]
Goodness, where could she be?
[AOI] It's kinda weird for
Mizuki to be late like this.
I wonder if she's okay.
[MIZUKI]
Sorry I'm late, honey.
[MIZUKI chuckles]
[ASHLEY]
How did everyone's day go?
We all finished our career
counseling, right?
[AOI]
Yeah.
[ASHLEY] Anything happen
in your meeting, Aoi?
[AOI] I'll be working in
the same office as before.
How 'bout you, Yuko?
I don't know.
There are so many options.
[AOI]
You're not gonna join ALCA?
It's a bit hard to explain,
but I formed my covenant
during the latter half
of my time at Pirari Academy.
Not just that.
The real problem is...
I'm a little afraid of fighting.
I can't help it.
I know it sounds silly,
but it's how I feel.
You're not still
undecided, are you?
You only have six months left.
You're an excellent student.
I'm sure if you went on
to join ALCA as a Logicalist,
you'd rise through
the ranks quickly.
Several offices have already
expressed interest in you.
I know, but still.
Is there another career choice
that you'd like to pursue?
ALCA is not your only option.
Many other students
continue their education
at regular universities.
Come now.
Those are students who haven't
even formed a covenant yet.
Miss Morigaya has some
of the best grades
in the S-Class.
She can't throw
away her potential,
even if the world is at peace.
You see, the thing is...
Nothing. Nevermind.
Please, feel free
to share your thoughts.
After all, it is your future
we're talking about here.
This school will be happy
with whatever decision
you choose to make
as long as you're happy.
Do whatever feels right to you.
Graduation is just
around the corner,
so this is the ideal time
for you to be thinking
about your plans.
And I'll always be here if
you need to talk about them.
Thanks. I appreciate that.
[ASHLEY]
Everything'll be okay, Yuko.
Remember, you still
have half a year left.
Plenty of time
for you to decide.
[YUKO]
Well, enough about me.
Thanks for listening.
So what are your plans, Mizuki?
[gasps] This is very unusual.
You don't normally show
that much interest
in my life.
It's okay if you don't
want to share with us.
If you want to know that badly,
I'll do you a solid
and let you in on it.
I've nothing to hide.
And since my plans are so grand
you're bound to
find out eventually.
So what are you up to?
An ALCA revolution.
Let's make sure the school
festival is really fun.
Oh, yeah!
It will be!
Don't act like you
didn't hear me!
And just what exactly is this
grand revolution of yours?
Since the world
is so peaceful now,
I'm afraid that danger
may lurk in the shadows.
Huh?
In the past, we all
faced a mutual threat.
Invasions from outside forces.
That's why the world
came together,
but what now?
Just the smallest
misunderstanding
could lead to all of humanity
fighting amongst ourselves.
That's what really scares me.
And if that comes to pass,
then Logicalists
with strong powers
will certainly be
dragged into the fighting.
But I have a solution!
ALCA should put its
efforts into functioning
as a system that exists
to maintain balance
across our world.
And that's my
vision of the future.
Well that certainly
is a grand plan.
I've always said
that the only dreams
worth chasing are the ones
that're hard to catch.
The president is actually
being serious for once.
[ASHLEY] I hope she
comes back to us soon.
Oh, give me a break!
I'm serious all
the time, you guys!
[GIRLS laugh]
[MIZUKI]
Why are you laughing?
[YUKO]
My dreams for the future.
Until recently,
I thought my only
choice was to join ALCA.
[YUKO]
When I was a little girl,
I wanted to be a pastry chef.
After that, I wanted
to be a florist.
And even a famous pop
star at one point.
Back in those days,
I had so many dreams.
Hey. Where's Yuko?
[AOI]
Yuko! What's the matter?
[knocking]
[YUKO]
Coming.
Goodness.
[MIZUKI] Hey. Let's take a
trip back to our childhood.
How many years has it been?
Since we last lit fireworks?
We were just little
kids the last time.
So maybe twelve
or thirteen years.
Nuh-uh! That can't be right.
I thought we lit some
before entering this school?
Were you with us?
[MIZUKI coughs]
Well, in any case...
You and I sure do have
a lot of history together.
[YUKO] Yeah, the two of us
have been in the same class
since kindergarten.
[MIZUKI]
So many years.
I remember when you
formed your covenant.
I was so envious.
[YUKO]
No. My power isn't special.
It's definitely not
suited for battle.
Aw, don't say that.
You have an amazing power.
You should be proud.
Now I was another story.
Forming a covenant
took me forever.
The whole ordeal
was so frustrating.
But looking back,
I know it's what made me
who I am today, and I'm
very thankful for that.
You're such an amazing person.
You truly think so?
Yes, because you've
already got your life goals
in sight and know
exactly how you're going
to achieve them.
But I'm nowhere near that level.
I still haven't found a
dream for myself quite yet.
[sighs]
I wonder what I'm supposed
to do with my life.
[MIZUKI]
But that's easy.
What do you want to do?
[YUKO]
Huh?
It's no fun if you
think of your future
as some sort of duty,
like you only have
one path to follow.
You're better off thinking
about what you want,
and what you want to do.
There's no greater
motivation than simply
doing what you like, is there?
[YUKO]
What I like?
[MIZUKI]
Uh, hey, Yuko.
I know that this
stuff's important,
but how 'bout a little
change of pace?
[YUKO]
A Bon Dance contest?
I wanna ask if you'll make
my dreams come true.
Can I take you? Just us.
On a yukata date--
[LION]
There you are, Yuko!
Goodness gracious.
I wasn't expecting you.
I know!
But I couldn't wait
another day to see you!
[YUKO]
Welcome home.
What perfect timing.
It turns out there's going
to be a Bon Dance
competition tomorrow.
--Let's invite everyone.
--[LION] Yay!
[MIZUKI]
Yuko, don't go!
[YAYOI] If you don't finish
your homework,
then you'll never even get
to start your Bon Dance!
[GROUP]
Yeah.
[YAYOI] Gosh! Try to
put some spirit into it.
[GROUP]
Yeah.
[MAHIRO] And we still have to
prepare for the school festival.
[LION]
Ya!
[YAYOI] You can do that after
you finish your homework.
Is there a reason why Lion
doesn't have to be over here?
That's because I've already
finished my homework.
And it was really tough.
You're not going anywhere!
[YUKO]
Goodness gracious.
You sure are working hard.
How 'bout you ladies take
a little break for a snack.
Here.
[YAYOI]
Thanks, Yuko.
I appreciate your concern.
I'll hold on to the food
and make sure
everyone's taken care of.
You can have one rice ball after
you finish that drill book.
[MAHIRO]
I can't wait that long!
I'll starve to death!
[YAYOI] So, what kind
of fillings did you put
in these rice balls?
[YUKO]
Oh, let me think, uh...
Hey, look, it's Nina!
What are you doing with that?
[LION]
Oh, this? It's the Bon Dance.
My daddy taught me how to do it.
[NINA]
Uh...
[LION]
Is something wrong?
I'm pretty sure that's
not the Bon Dance.
[LION]
Huh?!
[STRAFANSKY] Your daddy
knows what he's doing!
[MAHIRO]
I'm done.
[LION]
Here. You did a great job!
We can tell you
worked really hard.
[MAHIRO]
I'm gonna take a break now.
You've earned one.
[YAYOI] We'll be done
over here soon too.
[YUKO]
Well, what do you think, Lion?
Should we go ahead
and get changed?
Yeah!
[YAYOI] Oh, my, those flower
patterns are quite lovely.
They are.
Yeah. They're really cute.
Your bunny rabbits are adorable!
Hey. So who do you girls
think is gonna win
this thing anyway?
Win what?
The Bon Dance contest, duh.
It has a long history,
and every year
the big winner is
awarded a nice prize.
[KARIN] Not to brag or
anything, but our mistress
was the 92nd winner
of the competition.
[LION]
Really? That's amazing, Yayoi!
Then could you please
teach Lion the dance?
[LION] What? I already
know the Bon dance!
We don't have time,
but I will show her
before next year's.
That's so sweet of
you to help her out.
[train horn]
[MAHIRO]
The train's pulling up.
Look at all the delicious food!
[BELLE squeaks]
[NINA]
Hold on.
[LION]
What's wrong?
I just don't want you...
to get lost.
[LION]
Okay!
C'mon, Nina! Let's go!
[NINA] Wait a second,
there's no need to run.
Something wrong?
Do you need me to eat
that snack for you?
Please don't.
It's so cute that I wanna
take it home and keep it.
[LION] Would you like
some cotton candy?
[LION]
It's yummy.
[NINA]
So sweet.
I told you it's good.
[YUKO]
Hey, Lion! Nina!
Let's eat this tasty
takoyaki together!
[LION]
She's got a big plate of it!
[laughs]
[NINA] You're getting
a little too excited!
Say "ah."
Delicious!
[YUKO]
I knew you'd lke it!
Festivals always have
the best food, don't they?
Now, why don't you
have a bite, Nina?
[YUKO]
Here you go.
Have another one.
[LION chuckles]
[CHAIRWOMAN 7A] We managed to
have another splendid festival
this year thanks to
the Tachibana family.
Thank you so much
for your support.
I'm truly honored to
have been of service.
It's almost time for the
competition to get started.
Really?
[STAFF MEMBER 7A]
We have a crisis right now!
[CHAIRWOMAN 7A]
What's the matter?
[STAFF MEMBER 7A]
It's bad.
The medal for first
place has disappeared!
[YAYOI]
What is this?
Black feathers?
[KAREN]
They're all over the table!
This is very puzzling.
But no Tachibana
sponsored event will have
such an unfortunate ending.
Karin. Karen.
--Let's go search for it!
--[KARIN, KAREN] Roger!
[LION]
Are you gonna eat all that?
--Oh, Lion.
--What's going on?
Why are you in such a hurry?
The truth is that the grand
prize for the competition
has been stolen.
And we're trying
to quickly locate it.
Don't you worry.
I can help you look for it.
[BELLE squeaks]
We should always
help a person in need.
I'm touched.
And of course,
I'll gladly accept your help.
[GIRLS gasp]
[YAYOI]
That's it!
Okay, everyone, look at this!
These feathers were left
all over the crime scene.
And my guess is that the
black bird who just flew by us
has something
to do with the crime.
[MAHIRO]
Score, score, score!
A Foreigner response?
We'd better Trance
just to be safe.
[NINA]
Gate Access!
Tetra-Heaven!
[NINA]
Let's do this, Michael.
[MICHAEL] Feel free to use my
power as much as you need.
[YAYOI]
Gate Access! Disfia!
[YAYOI] I need your help
finding that medal, Qipao.
[QIPAO] That should be
easy if you use my power.
Uh-oh.
Did something happen to
the Foreigner response?
Yeah, my machine isn't
picking it up anymore.
[NINA]
Could it be?
I knew it.
[NINA] Is this the medal
you were looking for?
[YAYOI]
Yes! That's it!
I can't believe you
found it so quickly, Nina!
[KARIN]
Excellent!
Now the Bon Dance
competition can go on
just like you planned.
[MAHIRO]
That's awesome!
[LION]
Yay!
[YUKO]
Thank goodness.
[MIZUKI] Hush! I don't
want Yuko to see me!
[LION]
It's the president!
What are you doing
all the way up there?
[MIZUKI]
Stop! Don't come any closer!
Hang on. Do you need
help getting down?
I've got ya!
[MIZUKI]
Shoo!
[LION]
What'd you say?
Whoa, Nina.
What's wrong with you?
[NINA]
I really shouldn't say.
Can you explain the
sudden change of attitude?
[KAREN] Well, something happened
'cause your face is bright red.
Don't worry about me.
Go rescue Lion.
Why are you bringing
Lion into this problem?
Oh, now that you mention
it, where is she?
Oh! Why's she up there?
[NINA]
No! You can't go!
[YUKO]
Jeez! What's going on?
It's about what's
under her yukata.
[NINA]
Mumble mumble mumble.
She's buck naked!
[YAYOI]
Shh!
[YAYOI] How could she not
have worn underwear?
[KARIN] Let's not forget
that Japanese women
traditionally didn't wear
anything under their kimonos.
That's true, but Lion
would have no way
of knowing such a thing.
Wait... So who helped
her put on her yukata?
What's the problem?
It's normal not to
wear any. Isn't it?
[GROUP]
No way.
[KARIN] Wait, don't tell
me that you're also...
--[KAREN] Buck naked!
--[YAYOI] Karen!
Oh, no! The president
needs to see a doctor!
[NINA]
Um, Lion.
Try to climb with your
legs closer together
and come back down!
That was totally worth it.
Thank you, Yuko.
[crash]
[LION laughing]
[LION laughs]
Come dance with us, Nina!
I want you to dance with me.
But I'm fine just watching.
[YAYOI]
Japan has an old saying.
"You're going to be
a fool if you dance
and a fool if you just look on.
Either way you're a fool,
so you might as
well have a little fun."
Yeah, you're right!
[NINA]
Then I don't have a choice.
[MIZUKI] All I wanted was
to spend some quality time
with her.
Since this will be our
last summer break together.
[MIZUKI]
Yuko!
[YUKO] We used to eat
these ices all the time
when we were little.
[MIZUKI]
Yeah.
[YUKO]
You know what, Mizuki?
I've been giving it
some more thought,
and I find myself
having the most fun
when I'm looking after
Lion and all her friends.
When I see their smiling faces,
I feel happiness from
the bottom of my heart.
If possible, I'd like
to watch over them
as they grow older.
To help them reach
their full potential.
I guess that doesn't really
count as a dream though,
does it?
Come on.
I think that's a
splendid dream to have.
Thanks a lot.
You're sweet.
[YUKO]
Look!
It's Lion and her friends.
[YAYOI]
Control yourself!
[MIZUKI]
Uh-oh.
--[NINA] Please, Lion.
--[MIZUKI] Everyone will see.
[NINA]
Don't run around like that!
[KAGURA] Summer break will
be over before we know it.
[RINO]
Don't remind me.
[KAGURA]
You sound upset.
[RINO] I'm depressed that
I didn't get to do the things
I wanted to.
I couldn't go to the beach,
or the hot springs,
or the mountains,
or see any fireworks.
[KAGURA] Didn't you say
the same thing last year?
[RINO]
But what really gets me down
is that most people
think teachers
get the same kind
of fun summer break
all the students do.
Our schedules are so
packed that "summer break"
is actually busier
than the school year,
what with the training courses
and curriculum writing.
[KAGURA]
That's true.
[RINO] I even got a cute
new bathing suit this year.
[KAGURA]
Let's go swimming next weekend.
Are you serious?
That's amazing!
My first trip to the
beach this year! Ah!
[KAGURA] Well, you're kind of
easy to please, aren't you?