[MAID 9A]
Anna, Ellina, and Leasya.
Deploy to the specified area.
[STRAFANSKY]
Initiating Phase 2.
Our top priority
is securing the target!
Your Highness!
Yes, what is it?
There's an urgent letter.
Where is it from?
It says Japan, Your Highness.
Is that so?
[MAID 9A]
Target's been spotted.
Commencing operation.
[FEMALE BUTLER 9A]
What's wrong, Your Highness?
I've been called away.
I leave this mission
in your hands.
What could be so urgent
that you have to go now?
[STRAFANSKY] My presence
is required elsewhere.
A school festival.
A school festival?
[STUDENT chattering]
[YAYOI]
Okay, ladies!
We all have a lot of work to do
in a very short amount of time,
but please don't
cut any corners.
[YAYOI]
Karin!
--[YAYOI yelling]
--[KARIN crying]
[NINA]
Are you--really a witch?
[LION]
The people of this strange world
say that name
whenever they see me.
[MAHIRO]
Cut!
Lion, you are way off again.
[BELLE whines]
You need to get into character.
Try acting like a Foreigner
who's lost on Septpia.
[BELLE squeaks]
[LION]
Okay.
[MAHIRO]
Let's take five everybody.
I'm a Foreigner
who's gotten lost.
--[footsteps]
--I'm a Foreigner
--who's gotten lost.
So this is where
you've been hiding.
[LION]
Oh, hey.
[NINA] Mahiro asked me
to come find you.
[LION] I guess it's time
to rehearse again.
Sorry.
Why are you apologizing?
Because I'm dragging
everyone else in the play down.
You're just nervous because
people are looking at you.
Let's talk to Mahiro.
We'll tell her
we wanna practice alone.
Really?
Thanks a lot!
[LION giggles]
What an interesting young lady
you turned out to be.
Now drink some of this
morning dew!
It will help quench your thirst!
Just stop for a second.
What'd I do wrong now?
[NINA] It's the same problem--
your speech sounds unnatural.
Uh, well, I thought
the best way
to show that she was
from a different world
is to have my
Foreigner character
talk a little bit weirder
than the people of Septpia.
I get that, but you're
way overthinking it.
[LION]
Are you sure?
[NINA]
Listen.
The way you're reading
the role now isn't working.
Try acting as if the girl in the
play is actually you instead.
[STUDENTS chattering]
[KARIN] Mistress,
the props are halfway done,
but we're
running low on supplies
and need to go shopping
if we hope to finish on time.
Sorry, but the costumes
are taking us
longer than we expected.
The set builders are
having a lot of trouble.
Where do you want
lighting and sound set up?
[YAYOI] Things aren't moving
as smoothly as I'd planned.
The path to great theater's
a harsh one.
[BELLE squeaks]
[sighs]
I'll leave the actors'
performances to you,
Director Mahiro.
Roger that.
And I trust you to handle
all the behind-the-scenes work.
I intend to
meet those expectations.
But I really wish we all had
a little more time on our hands.
No kidding, the acting's
still got a long way to go.
Things are gonna
get pretty rough
if we can't figure stuff out.
I just thought of
the perfect idea.
[BELLE squeaks]
I propose extended prep hours!
There's no way we'll
make it at this rate!
--[RINO sighs]
--[KAGURA] Oh yeah?
[school bell chimes]
[KOZUE] This is a
special announcement.
Starting tomorrow after school
and ending
the following morning,
we will be open for students
to stay overnight
and prepare for the festival.
[STUDENTS]
Yay!
[KOZUE]
Please use your time wisely,
so that we may open
the first school festival
in tip-top form.
It's so on tomorrow!
Yay! Whoo!
That's a relief, huh?
Now we can practice
all night long.
Huh?
Huh...?
[STUDENTS chattering]
Just move it over
a little more to the right!
Wow! Look at that banner.
[BELLE squeaks]
Miss Pirari?
[LION]
Do you think it's possible
that the two of us
could ever be friends?
Because I'd like
to have a friend.
That's not right.
I know how this girl feels.
[LION hums]
[LION giggles]
[LION]
You're it, Mr. Bear!
[LION laughs]
Do you think it's possible that
the two of us could be friends?
[NINA]
Of course.
But is there a reason
you're asking?
It's just--
I haven't had a friend
in a very long time.
[NINA]
You said those lines perfectly.
[LION]
Really?
[NINA]
Just keep saying them like that.
[STUDENTS chattering]
Let's get through this
without any hiccups, ladies!
[STUDENTS cheer]
[KARIN yells]
[KAREN yells]
Everybody's been
working so hard.
And the Miss Pirari
contest's a hit.
I wonder who's gonna win.
Yeah, it's a total mystery.
[MAHIRO] Now all that's
left to fix is the acting.
Time to show 'em I got better!
You sure practiced a lot.
Yup!
Huh?! I'm excited
to see what you've got!
Do you think it's possible
that the two of us
could ever be friends?
[MAHIRO groans]
No matter how much I beg, the
god of acting won't visit Lion.
[NINA] But you said
the lines right yesterday.
We only have the auditorium for
a limited amount of time today.
So, how about you Trance
and try the scene again?
[LION]
Sure...
I trust you're
a girl of your word,
and you haven't forgotten
your promise to me.
I haven't.
Then you know.
It's meaningless
to rely on me and my power.
This is the performance
I've been dreaming about!
Really? That's how
you want me to act?
Yes, it was perfect!
[LION]
Yay!
Let's rehearse it again
really fast before I forget!
I trust you're
a girl of your word
and that you haven't forgotten
the promise you made to me.
[STUDENTS whine]
--She's bad again--
--Well, we don't have a choice.
Lion's gonna have to do
the entire performance
while Tranced with Rosa.
[MIZUKI]
Attention all Pirari students!
Today's the day you've all
been working so hard for!
It's the very first
Pirari Festival
our school has ever hosted.
So, it's not an
exaggeration to say that
the success of today's events
rides on each and
every student here.
Therefore, I ask that we all
take a moment to consider
the significance of
Septpia's coexistence
with alternate worlds,
with respect to Pirari's
foundation and history.
And to make sure we put on the
best school festival possible.
I invite everyone to have
as much fun as they can!
The first Pirari School
festival is now open!
[STUDENTS cheer]
Looks like things have started.
Our class performance
isn't until this afternoon,
so you're free to enjoy
the festival until then.
[STUDENTS cheer]
[CROWD chattering]
[BOOTH VENDOR 9A] Two grilled
Monoliums, coming right up!
So delicious!
But I wonder what
kind of meat this is.
Who cares?
We'll take two more.
Over here are the
villager costumes.
They're perfect.
And all the props are prepared.
The villagers all look good.
I can put those down
as completed.
How about the other costumes?
I can't believe there's
so much good food here!
I hope we can find
a nice spot to sit.
[BELLE squeaks]
--[LION gasps]
--Oh.
Welcome, ladies!
[LION]
Good morning, Yuko!
Is there a reason
you've Tranced?
[YUKO] Yes, our class is
hosting a Tetra-Heaven cafe.
Would you two like to come in
and join us for some tea?
Yup! If that's okay with Nina.
Sure.
What's that number one
badge for?
--[YUKO] Oh, this?
--[AOI] There she is!
Hey, Lion.
Do you mind wearing this badge
on your jacket for the day?
Goodness, looks like
you've been nominated
for the Miss Pirari Contest too.
So that's what these are for.
[BELLE whines]
[STRAFANSKY]
Behold! The angel of my country!
Isn't she cute?
Look at that adorable face!
Lion!
Please cast your vote
for my wonderful daughter.
Badge number six!
[MIZUKI] Pirari Academy's
number one beauty
will steal your heart!
Her name's Yuko Morigaya!
So hurry up and vote
for badge number one.
But remember that
Yuko belongs to me alone!
[STRAFANSKY yells]
[MIZUKI yells]
[BOTH yelling]
[BOTH groan]
[LINYA]
Hello, Honey.
[STRAFANSKY gasps]
What a surprise!
[LINYA] And don't worry,
the kitty cat is safe and sound.
[STRAFANSKY]
Wait! Let me explain!
[PRINCIPAL humming]
What are your thoughts on our
first ever school festival?
It looks like everyone
is enjoying themselves.
That's good. I was
a bit nervous since we've
never entertained
this many people before.
[CROWD chattering]
Look! Father and Mother
are both here.
I didn't expect
both of them to show up.
I see Mistress's mother
is in the audience too.
I guess her father must've
been too busy with work.
Come on, ladies!
We're having a pre-show meeting!
Understood.
[MAHIRO]
This is the real deal.
Thank you all for working
so hard on this project with me.
I hope that everyone
watching our play
will be more interested
in Foreigners
after hearing a song
from another world.
Here we go.
Let's give it our all out there!
[ALL]
Yeah!
[CROWD murmuring]
[buzzing]
Even though our village has
lost its only water source,
we can't let you go out
into the dangerous forest.
You'd only end up
being eaten by the witch!
Maybe. But if someone doesn't
go out and find water soon,
we'll surely all die of thirst.
[FEMALE STUDENT 9A] The well
dried up without warning
several days ago.
As far as we know, this might be
the work of that evil witch too.
[MAHIRO hooting]
This can't be.
If the forest brook's not here
then that means it
must've dried up too.
How will I get any water?
[LION] ♪ Many years
and months have passed ♪
♪ Since last I laid eyes
on my world ♪
♪ Yet I have a wish that lasts ♪
♪ Even with time
my hope never faded ♪
Please tell me who you are.
The people of your world
often call me a witch.
[NINA] What is that song
you were singing?
You heard?
[NINA]
Yes. It was beautiful.
Does that mean you're
really not afraid of me?
I can't let you collapse
out here in the forest.
The wild animals would love
nothing more than to eat you.
By showing me this spring,
you've saved my entire village.
Thank you so much.
You don't need to thank me.
This water's been one with the
earth long before I arrived.
It doesn't belong to me.
I refuse to believe
that you're really a witch.
An evil person wouldn't
have helped me like this.
What can I say.
That is what the people
of this world call me.
And I've never chosen
a different name.
You're such a mysterious girl.
Where did you come from?
Unlike you, this strange planet
we're on is not my home.
I came from another world.
[NINA]
How is that possible?
[FEMALE STUDENT 9C]
Look everybody, she came back!
Keep it up!
Your acting is spot on!
Leave everything
to me, director.
Just keep doing what you're
doing for the rest of the play!
[FEMALE STUDENT 9A]
It's water! Clean water!
[FEMALE STUDENT 9C]
She brought back water
from a running spring
found deep in the forest.
The village will
live on after all!
Here.
Thanks, Yayoi.
[YAYOI] I can tell you're
pretty nervous on stage.
Yeah.
A little but I'll be okay.
That's a good thing.
Nervousness comes from
the feelings one gets
when they really
want to succeed.
Or at least that's what
my great-great-grandfather
used to say.
Seeing you nervous
proves that you're
giving your very best today.
That means a lot.
This spring belongs to us now!
We won't let that
evil witch have it!
[STUDENTS]
We'll defend our water!
This awful drought has caused
every tree in the forest
to shrivel up and die.
This is bad!
This fire's getting
out of control!
At this rate,
the village will catch fire!
[FEMALE STUDENT 9A]
How can we stop it?
It can't be.
The village is burning.
[LION] There is a certain legend
told by the people of my world.
Can you tell it to me?
If two people
from separate worlds
come together peacefully
and join their hearts as one,
they can gain new powers and--
[gasps]
[groans]
[CROWD murmurs]
--Poor Lion!
--[CROWD murmurs]
[CROWD murmurs]
I-I don't know what I should do.
Oh no, Lion's lost her Trance.
What a disaster.
[LION whimpers]
Follow my lead.
Sing your song.
Let's save the village...
...together.
[LION]
Mm. I'd like that very much.
Together.
[LION, NINA] ♪ Many years
and months have passed ♪
♪ Since last I laid eyes
on my world ♪
♪ Yet I have a wish that lasts ♪
♪ Even with time
my hope's never faded ♪
♪ If you'll take my hand,
you'll hear it too ♪
♪ A soft and gentle voice ♪
♪ As long as I
stay close to you ♪
♪ Then both our hearts
will beat as one. ♪
♪ Show me a smile
There's no need for prayers ♪
♪ Your heart lets me know
that you care ♪
♪ A soul inside
that does beguile ♪
♪ Shines as bright as the sun ♪
♪ It calls out to me
It echoes inside ♪
♪ Keeping beat with my heart
just like a song ♪
[rain falls]
It's rain! The first rain
we've had in months!
And it's putting the fire out!
Do you think that pretty song
is responsible for this?
Which two girls could've
sung such a miraculous song?
One voice was from our village.
But what about the other singer?
Wow.
Maybe it's a goddess!
[STUDENTS]
It's the witch!
But this is the
so-called goddess
you were just talking about.
See, she's not an evil witch.
She's a friend
from a different world.
All she wants is
to live with us.
[applause]
--[CROWD cheers]
--[applause]
[STRAFANSKY sobs]
Bravo! Bravo!
[RINO giggles]
--[CROWD cheering]
--[STRAFANSKY crying]
--[STRAFANSKY] She's amazing!
--[CROWD cheering]
--That's my daughter!
--I love you!
[LION]
Mommy!
I'm so happy you came!
Lion! My sweet baby girl!
Nothing could've stopped me.
[LION giggles]
B-But Daddy came too.
Everyone was wonderful.
You get big gold stars.
[KAGURA]
Mm-hm.
[MAHIRO laughs]
--[YAYOI] What did I tell you...
--[MAHIRO] Good job.
[VERONICA]
Excuse me girls.
[NINA gasps]
Oh, hello, Bureau Chief.
I see that you're
fitting in at the academy.
Well, I'm trying to.
Please excuse me Chief,
but there're some people
who'd like to meet you.
[VERONICA]
Nina.
Enjoy your school life.
Were you just talking to
Bureau Chief Veronica?
She's amazing!
I've never seen her
in person before.
Hey, the big award ceremony's
just about to start!
Nina, you look upset.
Is there something wrong?
No, it's nothing.
We better go.
[STUDENTS chattering]
[MIZUKI]
The votes have been counted,
and now it's time to crown our
fist ever Miss Pirari Academy.
[gasps] And the winner is...
...entry number one,
Yuko Morigaya!
--[STUDENTS cheering]
--Huh?
--The election was rigged!
I really won?
You're so charming that
nobody else ever stood a chance!
Congratulations.
[AOI] We'll now announce the
winner of the stage division.
[STUDENTS chattering]
[YAYOI]
It took a lot of hugging,
but Lion's father
finally stopped crying.
And it didn't take long
for Lion to cheer up too,
once he quit making a scene.
[YAYOI] It's too bad that
we only got second place.
But I think everybody
understood the message
you were trying to get across
with that Foreigner song.
And of course,
the same goes for me.
[YAYOI]
Hm?
[MAHIRO snoring]
[YAYOI] Thanks for all
your hard work, Mahiro.
[STRAFANSKY]
This is my wife. Ha, ha, ha!
[RINO] So now we have Lion's
mother to deal with too.
I'm sorry about my husband.
He's caused you all
so much trouble.
[KAGURA]
Nothing less from a First Lady.
[KOZUE] The other teachers
and I have often wondered
what made you fall in love
with Lion's father.
Good question. I'm curious.
[KOZUE]
Is it what I'm thinking?
You know what I'm
getting at, right?
[RINO]
You're being so vague
that I have no idea
what you're hinting at.
[LINYA]
Let me think.
Well, it was a
combination of things.
But I think what really
sealed the deal for me
was his promise to always
spend birthdays together.
He would bring me roses,
no matter what battlefield
I was fighting on.
[KOZUE] That would definitely
set my heart aflutter.
It worked for me!
[RINO]
That's sweet,
but I'm gonna need
all the juicy details!
[LINYA, STRAFANSKY]
Uh--