[RINO] Everyone, the repairs
at the training grounds
have been completed.
You'll be able to use them again
starting tomorrow morning.
Does that mean we can finally
take our practical exam?
While I'd like to give you
a gold star for your dedication,
I'm afraid not.
After all, the closing
ceremony's next week.
[gasps]
That's disappointing.
Nah, we're better off
without that test anyway.
Now, Mahiro!
The practical exam only
comes but twice a year, and--
[KAGURA]
Yayoi.
Please let us continue on
with homeroom.
[YAYOI]
Pardon me, Miss Kagura.
[KAGURA] I have news regarding
the New Year's incident.
Since the entire class was
involved, I'll say it here.
Lion.
Yes.
[KAGURA]
Nina.
Yes, ma'am.
[KAGURA] You two
will not be reprimanded.
[LION sighs]
[ALL sigh]
But Lion will continue
her after school lessons,
for at least a few months.
I trust you know why.
I do.
[KAGURA] And Nina, please come
to the staff room after class.
That's all.
Understood.
[STUDENTS chattering]
[KAGURA]
For you.
From Bureau Chief Veronica.
She wants to interview you
after the graduation ceremony.
Seems ALCA believes the
actions you took to save Lion
were quite admirable.
[NINA]
But that was--
I assume you'll be going
back to your post at ALCA--
[KAGURA]
Fujisaki.
[RINO]
Oh, I'm sorry.
I shouldn't have
jumped to conclusions.
This is an important matter,
so take time to think it over.
[YAYOI] I declare a
state of emergency!
Mistress, you might wanna
lower your voice just a little.
[YAYOI]
I can't!
Not when our Nina's
about to return to ALCA!
Well, actually,
it's more accurate to say that
she might be rejoining ALCA.
Nina was an active member.
You guys need to fill me in
on what's happening.
Well judging from her
conversation with the teachers
that we happened to overhear,
ALCA was quite impressed
with Nina rescuing Lion.
Obviously I don't know the story
on why she came to our school,
but shouldn't this be considered
as good news for her?
Indeed.
You're absolutely right.
Nina's reinstatement should be
looked at as a good thing.
But, it's just--
This is all just
so sudden, you know?
No denying that.
And if Nina goes
along with their plan,
she might not stay with us
'til graduation.
What? I don't wanna hear that,
you're making me sad.
It's very sad.
Indeed, it is.
I'm really bummed out.
[BELLE squeaks]
[LION]
I'm happy for her.
Seriously?
This is great!
I'm sure Nina is
jumping for joy as we speak.
[LION]
Yup. Everything's great.
Good news.
--[BELLE squeaks]
--[LION groans]
Whoa, are you okay, Lion?
Yeah, I'm fine.
[door closes]
Great, now we have to
worry about her too.
Well, she is the one who
loves Nina the most, after all.
I wonder if Nina
has any intention of
staying enrolled at the academy.
I don't have any idea.
Of course, if she really does
want to return to work at ALCA,
then the issue is
out of our hands.
But, what if we could
somehow make Nina feel as if
she'd be better off staying here
and continuing her studies?
For what it's worth,
I'd be much happier if she
decided to stay at Pirari.
Me too!
Count me in too, Mistress!
[KAREN]
All right!
Yeah, I think that's gonna
be a pretty rough feat.
[MAHIRO]
Huh?
Goodness gracious.
Did you need something, Lion?
[LION] Getting ready
to move, huh, Yuko?
That's right.
I have to be out of my dorm room
after I graduate next week.
Better pack while I can.
Oh, I see.
It's sad knowing we won't be
together any longer, isn't it?
Are you really gonna miss us?
Well, of course.
But you're lucky to still have
Yayoi, Mahiro, and Nina
by your side, right?
[BELLE squeaks]
And don't forget Belle.
[LION]
You're right!
Huh?
[LION giggles]
Sounds like I'll be just fine.
Thanks for your help, Yuko!
[BELLE squeaks]
My goodness.
Isn't the cafeteria food
here absolutely delicious?
Oh, yeah!
And all the fresh ingredients
are grown in Pirari Town.
In my book,
the definition of happiness
is eating food
this good every day.
What do you think, Nina?
Huh? Yeah, I guess you're right.
Considering all our
options at school,
I bet you wouldn't find anything
this good at, let's say, ALCA.
[KAREN] And Yuko's sweets
are totally amazing!
Shirakaba Dormitory
really is the best!
I'm so happy that you've
been enjoying my snacks.
Karen!
We won't be able to
eat her sweets anymore!
Oh! That's right.
She's graduating soon.
I sure am.
But I promise to make you girls
plenty of yummy
treats until then.
[KAREN]
Score!
Thanks a lot, Yuko!
When I was made resident advisor
and given the responsibility
to look after you all,
I was really worried that
I wouldn't be up to the task.
But you're all such good girls
that I ended up
having a lot of fun!
Thank you for that.
[YAYOI]
You're so nice, Yuko.
Graduation's the day
after tomorrow, eh?
That really came fast.
Only two days away.
It'll be sad to go
our separate ways,
but we have no choice.
You're right.
Life goes on.
[KAREN] I guess our "Entice Her
with Yummy Food" plan failed.
[KARIN]
Yeah, and that "it'll be sad
to go our separate ways" line
was clearly about her
leaving all of us.
[YAYOI] I'm impressed you
noticed she said that.
Well don't forget that observing
people is my specialty.
That's my sharp sister for you!
Now then, it's time to
carry out our next plan.
[MAHIRO]
What are those for?
[YAYOI] Pictures of our
enjoyable memories
together with Nina are sure
to move her heart in our favor.
[gasps]
[LION] Huh? Oh, it's
a picture of Nina!
[giggles] Cool!
This one's of Nina too.
Here she is again!
And here's another one!
Awesome!
It's a Nina hallway!
[ALL]
Uh...
So many cute pics of her!
Check our "Memories are Eternal"
plan off as a complete failure.
Do you have any
good ideas, Mahiro?
It'd be a lie to say I don't.
Ta-da!
Mr. Scorpion-Tail is on it!
[screams]
[LION]
What's happening?
What's going on out here?
Goodness gracious.
[cries]
Tough luck. That was a bust.
[LION giggles]
[sighs] The water's
nice tonight, isn't it?
Yeah.
Mahiro and Yayoi sure are
taking their time though.
I guess they are.
[YUKO]
I wonder what's holding them up.
[YAYOI] Gosh, why do you
always, always, always
have to make such
strange devices?
[MAHIRO laughs]
Don't think you can simply
laugh this disaster off.
I can tell you're
not into our plans.
So you figured me out.
Why don't you care?
If going back to ALCA leads
to Nina fulfilling her dreams,
I think we should let her go.
Well of course we all
agree with you on that point.
That's why we're
carrying out these schemes
in such a roundabout way.
If I knew staying here
was the right thing,
I'd do everything
in my power to stop her.
And on top of that, I still
haven't had a chance
to beat Nina yet.
My plan had been
to settle things with her
during the winter
practical exams.
Well, in that case!
[knocking]
[NINA]
Come in.
Hey, Nina.
You wanna look at these
together? You should.
There's lots of
awesome shots of you!
[NINA]
Oh, so those pictures are yours?
Nope. I found them
in the hallway.
I wonder who they belong to.
I tried my best to find out,
but nobody knew whose they were.
Do you think it's
wrong of me to keep them?
If you can't find
the rightful owner,
then it's perfectly fine
for you to hold on to them.
Then that's what I'll do.
[LION] Wasn't the
Pirari Festival so much fun?
[NINA]
Yeah.
[LION] I should have nominated
you for the Miss Pirari Contest.
You didn't need to do that.
But you could've won.
That's not true
Oh, c'mon.
[NINA] There was no way
I would've gotten picked.
--[thud]
--[LION yells]
[NINA] Remember how pretty
the cherry blossoms were?
You love cherry blossoms.
I do.
I thought the ones we saw that
day ware particularly beautiful.
Do you know the school has a
path lined with trees like that?
I love when they're
all in full bloom.
It's kinda magical.
That does sound nice.
Guess you haven't gotten
the chance to see them?
No.
I was really surprised to find
you passed out on the walkway
on your first day of school.
[laughs]
Believe me, I was
super surprised too.
When I woke up and
found you staring at me.
[BOTH laugh]
[MAHIRO]
Good morning.
[YAYOI]
Good morning to you as well.
Wow. Isn't this a rare sight?
You never get out
of bed on your own.
I needed time to get pumped up
and prepped for later today.
Our great mistress is one thing!
But it's a terrible shame
getting beat by Mahiro!
So, you finally made it.
We're in the
preliminary rounds now.
Are you guys
serious about this?
[YAYOI]
Of course, we are.
And whoever wins
this next battle
gets to challenge you
to a championship match.
Why don't you both
come at me at once?
[NINA]
Gate Access.
Tetra-Heaven!
[NINA]
They're pretty strong, Michael.
[MICHAEL]
Yes.
But we'll take them both on
as a powerful knight!
I hope you don't think I'm gonna
roll over and let you beat me.
You'd better give it your all.
Let's do this thing.
[NINA] I wasn't
expecting to fight today.
The results of this
year's summer practical
just won't do!
We have no choice but to
take on the strongest student!
We must protect our honor!
[MAHIRO yells]
But I'm not the
strongest one in our class.
I lost to Lion
just like everyone else.
I can challenge her to a
mock battle any time I want.
[YAYOI grunting]
But this is the last chance
we're ever gonna get
to settle the score with you!
[YAYOI] You can't just
win and run away!
I'd never allow that!
Huh?
What are you two talking about?
[YAYOI grunts]
--Why don't you fight back?
--[MAHIRO] Take this seriously!
[NINA]
Logic Drive!
[BOTH gasp]
[BOTH scream]
[YAYOI, MAHIRO whine]
[door opens]
[LION]
Hey, Nina.
I knew you'd be up here
looking at stars.
Yeah.
[LION]
So pretty.
[NINA] It is, but soon we won't
be able to see Orion anymore.
So tomorrow's the day.
Graduation.
Yeah.
Can you believe it?
Are you okay?
Yeah, everything's just fine.
[STUDENTS chattering]
We ladies couldn't be more proud
of our most beloved graduate!
Yeah, and we got you
some flowers!
Thank you so much, everyone!
Congratulations on graduating.
Thanks a lot, Ashley.
If you would have told me
on the first day we met
how interesting our school life
would end up being,
I never would've believed you.
Yeah, you're right.
We've had lots of twists and
turns from a certain person.
[STUDENTS chattering]
Now, now, tears don't suit a
lovely lady such as yourself.
Oh, Mizuki.
I'm sure gonna miss
all your great jokes.
I have to say,
it's been a lot of fun.
Yeah.
[laughs]
[MIZUKI]
Ready to go, Yuko?
Yup.
Excuse me, but are you two...
[YUKO giggles]
I was recently assigned
to the same ALCA office
as my dear friend, Mizuki.
What a handful, huh?
[YUKO]
Now take care, everyone.
[MIZUKI]
Wait a second.
I'm a handful?
Does that mean
you don't like me?
I just realized that I
haven't seen Lion today.
[STUDENTS chattering]
Yuko, are you seeing this?
[YAYOI]
Nina, wait!
[NINA panting]
[gasps]
Uh, Miss Alexandrovna?
Lion?
[NINA]
There you are!
[LION]
Hey, Nina.
Why did you do this
to the cherry blossoms?
[LION]
Don't they make you happy?
You said these trees
were beautiful in bloom.
So, I wanted you
to see them again.
And that's because...
we'll be parting ways soon?
Yeah.
[NINA]
Because I'm going back to ALCA?
Yeah.
You know that's what
I've been working towards
this whole school year.
I wanted to go back.
I'm so sorry.
[LION]
Mm-mm!
No, I'm fine. Remember?
I promised to support you
no matter what path you choose.
[gasps]
And besides, I'm gonna
catch up to you in no time!
Well, maybe "no time"
is impossible.
So like, five years?
I guess it's actually gonna
take me a pretty long time.
But I'll get there eventually!
[LION sobs]
Come on, there's no need
for tears, silly.
[gasps]
Cheer up.
After meeting you
and everyone else here...
...how could I possibly leave?
This is where all my precious
friends are, after all.
[gasps]
Looks like Lion's done it again.
[BELLE squeaks]
Hi there, Belle.
I thought we had an agreement
that you'd look after her?
[BELLE squeaks]
[KAGURA sighs]
[KAGURA] So we'll be in charge
of those kids again next year.
Lots to look forward to.
If you say so.
[harp playing]
[BELLE squeaks]
Agreed.
Septpia can be quite fun,
can't it, little one?
[BELLE squeaks]
[PRINCIPAL] Everything
in this world is in flux,
spinning round a sun,
unaware of how to stop.
[BELLE squeaks]
[PRINCIPAL]
Yes, that's right.
Like a beautiful song coming
together, full of life.
It's the first time I've
ever seen cherry blossoms
at a graduation.
What's going to happen
during the entrance ceremony?
I imagine more pretty
flowers will be here.
A nice greeting
to our new little chicks.
[LION]
Take care, Yuko.
We wish you luck!
Goodness gracious,
you're in a good mood!
Yup!
Farewell!
[LION laughs]
[BOTH giggle]
Feels nice to be
your precious friend.
Don't forget that I meant
all of our other friends
were precious as well.
I know, but I'm still happy.
Can I ask you
a serious question?
Sure, what is it?
[NINA]
I was wondering,
what kind of Logicalist
do you want to be?
I've always wanted to be
one just like you, Nina.
And what exactly
do you mean by that?
Let's see, well,
I'd like to help people
who are in danger
and support those
who are trying their best
but need a little boost.
Kinda like how
you were there for me
when I needed a helping hand.
Would you like to do
anything different?
I'd like to continue down
the same path, for sure.
Protecting Septpia with the
special powers I've been given
for as long as I'm
able to Trance.
That's why I'm gonna stay here
and study all sorts
of different things.
And get stronger.
Maybe as strong as you.
Huh? Can you say
that last part again?
[NINA]
Forget it.
[LION]
C'mon, Nina! What was it?
[LION giggles]
[BOTH giggle]
[NINA]
What are all of you doing here?
We've been waiting for you.
Hoping that on the off chance
you changed your mind
about leaving us.
[NINA] I thought
I told you girls yesterday
that I planned on
staying here at school.
[MAHIRO] Are you really
okay with that decision?
Yes.
Because I realized
there's something important
I need to learn before I go.
Not to mention,
we're all here too.
What is that supposed to mean?
Well, you see,
[LION] Nina called all of us
her precious friends.
--[YAYOI] Oh, Nina!
--[MAHIRO] Nina!
--[KARIN] You're precious too!
--[KAREN] Yay!
Whoa, hold on a second--
I'm overflowing with joy!
This is what I call friendship!
[KARIN]
You're the absolute best!
I'm the what?
[gasps]
Have I ever told you
that I love you?
--[LION giggles]
--[OTHERS gasp]
[YAYOI]
Oh no!
[ALL scream]
[NINA gasps]
[NINA groans]
[NINA yells]
[ALL groan]
[YAYOI]
What were you thinking, Lion?
You're a handful.
--[LION giggles]
--[BELLE squeaks]