[PILOT 3A] At this speed, we'll
be entering Japan's airspace
in a few minutes.
We need to turn
this plane around now.
If we go any further,
we'll be violating the law.
It will cause an
international incident.
[STRAFANSKY]
Here is fine.
[PILOT 3A] It's been a honor
and a privilege to accompany
a living legend such as
yourself, Silver Grizzly.
[PILOT 3B]
Good luck, sir!
[PILOT 3A]
Our mission's complete.
Should we head back home now?
[PILOT 3B] Yeah, let's hurry
back and grab ourselves
some drinks.
[RINO] The known worlds
are Monolium, Disfia,
Tetra-Heaven, and Tritomy.
And then of course there's the
fifth one where we humans live,
Septpia.
[KAGURA]
My head hurts so bad.
This hangover is killing me.
[RINO]
As you should know by now,
ours is the only world
in which we may open Gates
that connect all
of them together.
[alarm blaring]
Was there an emergency
drill scheduled today?
I dunno, maybe.
What is that?
[BELLE squeaks]
Sounds like the air raid alarm.
No way.
Is it a Foreigner?!
[GIRLS gasp]
[RINO]
Don't panic!
Everyone just calm down.
Let's wait for instructions.
Hey, look!
There's something in the sky!
[BELLE squeaks]
Wait... Are you sure?
I can't see anything out there.
Do you really see something
flying towards us?
Mm-hmm. Right there.
Look where I'm pointing.
I am.
It's only a tiny little speck,
but it's getting
bigger and bigger.
Well, uh...
I'm not picking up any readings.
[ANNOUNCER] We've identified
an approaching missile.
I guess you really
did see something.
[LION]
Mm-hmm.
Miss Kagura!
Shouldn't you be evacuating us?
Calm down, Yayoi.
This school is
protected by ALCA.
It's impossible for a
conventional weapon to reach us.
[RINO] Our defense system is
programmed to automatically
destroy any unidentified
approaching object.
[RINO]
Did we get it?
Look at those guns!
[GIRLS chattering]
[RINO]
All right!
Everyone get back!
Now cover your ears because
it's going to get noisy.
Got ya.
[GIRLS scream]
[RINO]
She did it!
[KAGURA]
What the--?
That's strange.
You've gotta be kidding!
[BELLE squeaks]
What is that thing?
It's awesome.
[STRAFANSKY]
Lion!
Don't worry, class.
All the glass in these
windows has been reinforced.
Bullets can't break them.
So you'll be safe in here.
[RINO]
Here you go!
[LION]
Daddy! What are you doing?!
[YAYOI]
Daddy?
Lion! Sweetie!
Daddy missed you so much!
I brought you these!
Ah! Oh, no.
I picked each flower
myself just for you.
But I brought other
treats from home!
Lion, explain.
You must be my daughter's
homeroom teacher.
As expected, you're
very skilled in battle.
And you are?
Where are my manners?
Excuse me, my name is
Strafansky Yelistratova.
I'm Lion's father.
Cupcake. Please introduce your
daddy to all your new friends.
You're embarrassing me!
[STRAFANSKY]
What did I do?!
[KOZUE]
Sorry, sir.
But in the future we'd
very much appreciate
you contacting us
before visiting the school.
[STRAFANSKY]
I did contact you,
and I believe you were
the one who refused me.
Isn't that correct?
Mr. Yelistratova,
what I refused
was your request to live
in the dorm room
alongside your daughter,
but I never said that
you couldn't visit her.
Yeah, and that makes me angry!
Cut it out, Daddy!
You're causing trouble for
everyone here at school!
This is what I hate about you!
You hate me?!
Lion! But why?
What don't you get?
I just wanna be
with my baby girl!
What a bizarre man.
Compared to him,
Lion seems normal.
I'm still not getting
a Foreigner response.
Of course not,
he's obviously human.
And he's not a hybrid.
Because humans can't
reproduce with the Foreigners.
Aww. I was hoping he'd turn
out to be a new type
of Foreigner after I saw
how strong he is.
[LION]
I can't deal with you anymore!
[GIRLS yell]
What are you guys doing?
Really? Nina too?
Thanks for letting
us come inside.
Lion. Sweetheart. Baby.
I came all the way from
Liones just to see you!
Well that was a mistake!
Go home right now!
[yelling]
So what's Liones?
That's the name of
the great little country
where my beautiful
Liones hails from.
So you named her
after the country
she'll rule over one day?
That's kinda creepy,
don't you think?
[STRAFANSKY]
It's named after her, actually.
No one wants a father
who's too clingy.
Try giving her a
little space for once.
Your father would cry
if he heard you say that.
You are his precious baby.
Do you understand
what they're saying?
Sorry. Punkin. I'm so sorry!
Teens can be so
cruel to their fathers.
This unexpected visit
was especially dramatic,
to say the least.
It sure was!
We even had to fire off
anti-aircraft weaponry at him.
It felt good having a Stinger
back in my hand, though.
While I don't condone
the unconventional actions
that took place today...
I can definitely understand
how you feel, sir.
So we'll make an
exception this one time
and let you sit in
on Lion's lectures.
Thank you, Miss!
I'm so very grateful!
Thank you! Thank you!
[RINO] I know a lot of students
think that learning math
is a waste of time
for a Logicalist.
But these skills are
essential for planning
an effective battle strategy.
Let's see.
Ten kilometers away and moving
at a speed of 300, then, uh...
[STRAFANSKY]
Use your daddy's fingers!
And here, count my toes too!
[GIRLS laughing]
Sir, please.
I really need you to
be quiet during class.
Oh, I do apologize.
Looks like I got in trouble!
[LION groans]
[STRAFANSKY]
Lion!
Please don't leave me
all alone again!
Would you stop following me?
But you used to get lost
walking around your own castle.
I worry about you in this
giant labyrinth of a school.
Stay out here!
[STRAFANSKY]
Keep it up!
Move those legs!
[KAGURA]
After a Logicalist has Tranced,
they start experiencing
sudden increases
in their powers.
But each Logicalist
must decide on their own
how to use that power.
Don't think you can
rely on strength alone.
You'll never win
a battle that way.
[STRAFANSKY]
Combat skills are good,
but having a strong
defense greatly increases
your chance of success,
as I'm sure you'll agree,
Miss Kagura.
[BELLE squeaks]
[STRAFANSKY] I thought you might
be missing food from home.
So I asked your mother to
cook up all your favorites
and I brought them
along with me.
Go ahead and dig in!
Is it good?
Tastes just like home, right?
I actually helped your
mother make those kebabs.
[KARIN]
Aww. He's so nice.
What's the matter?
Keep eating!
This is all for you.
No. I'm done.
Come on, you love these
meatballs your mother makes.
No. Not really.
Your mother would be
very sad to hear that.
I'm not... hungry.
[STRAFANSKY] So you don't
have much of an appetite?
Well now. Take this.
The scent will make you relax
and help your appetite return.
Don't worry, I already
took the thorns off.
Stop! Just leave me alone!
Lion?
[KAGURA]
Start your Trance!
[MAHIRO]
Gate Access! Tritomy!
Let's do this, Selen!
[SELEN] Target located.
Executing mission.
[NINA]
Amol.
[AMOL]
Right.
[YAYOI]
Qipao!
[QIPAO]
Okay, okay.
[LION]
Rosa!
[ROSA]
Yes.
[RINO] Even though
this is a mock battle,
you have actually Tranced.
So please be careful.
[GROUP]
Got it.
I won't take another
defeat today, Nina!
Here I come!
[LION yelling]
[MAHIRO yells]
Lion! You're doing great!
Take her down!
Honey! Watch your feet!
Remember our roadwork?
We used to run
together every morning!
Step, step, step!
I miss how we used
to sing while we ran!
Come on!
Step, step, step, step!
[MAHIRO gasps]
[GIRLS gasp]
What'd I do to you?!
I don't want people
looking down on me.
So I'm just gonna have to
end this fight right now.
I'm not letting
you win that easily!
This won't hold me!
What are you doing?!
You're crazy!
That isn't fair at all!
Ha!
I'm using this missile to win!
[LION, NINA, YAYOI scream]
Huh?!
This is crazy!
Mistress, no!
[STRAFANSKY ]
Lion!
[YAYOI]
Well this is just great!
Why do you two always, always,
always have to cause trouble?
[LION, MAHIRO]
We're so sorry.
But it's not as if we can
do anything about it now.
So I say we just take it
easy until they find us!
You obviously fail to
understand the gravity
of the situation
you've put us in here.
Right, Nina?
So fluffy.
[YAYOI]
A bear cub?!
[MAHIRO]
He's pretty cute.
You know what?
We need to put some
distance between us and it.
Yes. Absolutely.
Let's back away quietly.
If the cub's parents
found us messing with it...
[GIRLS yell]
Uh... Nina.
I'm not an expert, but
I'm pretty sure this bear
wants its cub back.
[NINA]
So fluffy.
You know...
I've heard that mama bears
can be extremely ferocious
when it comes to
protecting their babies.
Yeah, that is true.
Daddy always warned me
to run away as fast
as I could if I saw
a grizzly with its cubs.
[YAYOI]
Mm-hmm.
Are you listening to us?
Why are you still holding
that bear's baby?!
C'mon, Nina!
Let go of that cub!
But it's so fluffy.
This is a translation machine.
This... blows on ramen.
No, not the radar!
[radar beeps]
A Foreigner?
Who cares about that? Run!
[LION]
But humans can't outrun bears!
Yes, that's the one!
This bear repellent machine
puts off a frequency
that they hate!
Switching it on now!
[GIRLS screaming]
[RINO]
We were tracking their movements
by monitoring
Belle's Paradox level.
But then about ten
to twenty minutes ago,
an avalanche struck
their last known location.
Avalanche?
Please let us come with you!
We have to go!
Sorry, girls.
But we can handle
this by ourselves.
What about Lion's father though?
Already left.
He headed straight north.
[STRAFANSKY] It is true that
Lion started demonstrating
high Logicalist powers
at a very young age.
But the reason I
established this country
was to protect her.
I stopped her from being
conscripted into ALCA.
So my answer's no.
I have no intention of
ever handing her over.
[PRINCIPAL]
We understand your concern, but
your daughter's like a
metronome without a tempo
right now.
Feeling lost.
Right.
And if Lion doesn't learn
how to use her powers,
she will cause a
catastrophe one day.
[STRAFANSKY]
She would never!
Please, you need to trust us.
For your daughter's sake.
[STRAFANSKY]
Lion.
Yeah.
This is a pretty deep crevasse
that we've fallen into here.
Nina, is there something
wrong with you?
You have a really high fever.
I'm scared we're all
gonna get sick in this cold.
If we're going to survive,
we have to do some--
[stomach growling]
I know now's not the
time, but I'm really hungry.
How can you think
about food at a--
[stomach growling]
[MAHIRO chuckles]
[STRAFANSKY]
Lion!
The roses!
There's no way
Daddy won't see these.
Now that's using
your brains, girl!
Nina can't wait much longer.
We need to get her
to the infirmary.
[growling]
Yes, we're all hungry,
but first--
--It's the bear!
--[LION] No!
And she looks angry!
We don't have anywhere to run!
You don't wanna eat us!
We're all nothing
but skin and bones!
Daddy!
[STRAFANSKY yells]
You're safe, baby.
I'm here.
Watch out!
[bear growls]
For Lion!
Oh, I see.
You're like me, aren't you?
Daddy!
[laughing]
Nina.
Where am I?
In your dorm room.
Just relax.
Everyone made it back
safe and sound.
[KARIN]
Mistress!
We were so worried!
Please promise you won't
ever go off like that
without us again, okay?
Cross my heart.
It will never happen again.
I kinda can't
believe we survived.
I'm sorry.
This is all my fault.
I shouldn't have come here.
Uh-uh.
You're not the one responsible.
Me being embarrassed
about you is what caused
this whole stupid mess.
I finally realized that you're
just worried about me, Daddy.
Yes!
You are such an angel!
Lion!
You understanding how
I feel makes me so happy.
[LION]
But listen.
You don't need to worry
about me anymore.
I've already made
so many new friends.
And that means no one is
alone because we're all here
for one another!
Right.
My baby's growing up.
I'm so proud of you!
I guess that means
you're gonna be fine
without your daddy
watching over you.
[stomach growling]
You hungry?
That home-cooked food.
I've still got it on me.
You want it?
Yeah!
[STRAFANSKY]
All right!
Then let's go back
to your dorm and eat!
I've no doubt your room
here is beautifully decorated.
Thanks a lot, Daddy.
Bye, now.
Why are you acting so
cold to me again, sweetie?
Well, our dorm is--
You're a man.
Sorry, but girls only.
[LION]
There's plenty for all of us!
Let's pig out!
I would be overjoyed to
sample some of the delicacies
from your homeland.
Karen. Karin. Prepare the table.
[STRAFANSKY]
No! No way!
Dasvidaniya!
[STRAFANSKY] I need a drink
after the day I've had!
What am I supposed
to do about Lion?
Please! Someone tell me!
When fathers act
needy like this,
their daughters start to grow
resentful towards them.
I'd be happy to
teach you some things.
Tell me.
Are you familiar with the
phrase "give and take"?
Of course I'm familiar.
What is it you desire?
[KOZUE] Perhaps a chance to
mingle with some single guys?
[STRAFANSKY]
I see what you're getting at.
You want me to host a social
event, like a mixer?
[RINO]
Mixer?
Do you really understand
what she wants?
[STRAFANSKY]
Leave it to me.
I know many celebrities
across the world.
[KOZUE]
Celebrities? That's amazing!
When's a good time for you?
[RINO] I'm available at the
beginning of next month!
[KOZUE]
Let's get everything set up!
What kind of hot
bachelors do you know?
[STRAFANSKY]
Let's see.
The Wolf of Siberia.
The Lightning of Kremlin.
Oh! And the Giant of Tiefu is
recently divorced and single!
[RINO] Those aren't
really celebrities--
they're soldiers, right?
[KOZUE]
I'm all for it!
Aren't strong guys
the absolute best?
[RINO]
I totally agree!
[STRAFANSKY]
Then let's toast to our mixer!
Give me another glass of
that sweet potato liquor!
[KAGURA]
You're fine with that?