I'll explode if
I eat another bite.
[KARIN] I thought this would be
like a luxurious resort.
[KARIN]
Impressive.
Lion's father is amazing.
Oh, yes, indeed.
[STRAFANSKY yelling]
[KARIN] It's hard to
believe he's a human.
[YAYOI]
Oh, yes, indeed.
You tend to get sleepy
when you're hot, right?
Oh, yes, indeed.
So tell me.
Did you like lunch today?
Oh, yes, indeed.
And you're good with doing
my summer homework for me?
You can do it yourself.
Aww.
[LINYA]
Sorry about all of this.
You came all the way out here
just when our air
conditioner broke down.
Oh! Please don't concern
yourself about that.
Everything's been perfect.
[LINYA] Yayoi, you are so polite
and have the best manners.
I hope Lion picks
some of that up.
Where'd she go this time?
That girl better not
have run away to avoid
doing her homework again.
[KARIN]
She didn't.
She went on a walk with Mahiro.
Is that right, Mistress?
Yes. Mahiro said something about
finishing off her free research.
I'm so glad she's studying.
But I wonder what part of the
country they're exploring.
[KARIN]
I don't know.
There's the beach.
Or the mountain.
They're in the forest.
[LION]
Faster than usual today.
[BELLE squeaks]
[LINYA]
When my Lion was a little girl,
she was so sensitive
and a bit of a crybaby.
I couldn't help but spoil her
and she never wanted
to leave my side.
Really?
But after so many adventures in
the wilderness with her father,
she turned into quite
a wild little monkey.
For the most part,
I did my best to
homeschool her myself.
But the only things
at which she excelled
were camping and fishing.
I really hope she's not been
much of a bother to you all.
I assure you that she's not.
Rather, I would say that...
Her father's the one
who's been a real handful.
Karin!
[LINYA]
Yes, you're right.
I know he was.
That's why I made sure to
give him a proper punishment
when he returned.
That kind of fiasco
won't happen again.
[STRAFANSKY gasps]
Bloodthirst?
Or so he promised,
but I know he forced
all of you to come to Liones
over your summer break.
Lord help me.
I just don't know how
to beat something
past that thick skull of his and
into his long-term memory.
Well now.
I wouldn't say he
forced us here.
Lion!
Daddy's here to pick you up!
Come on, grab your stuff
and I'll take you back home.
No.
And why not?
Your semester's over.
Your daddy and mommy miss
you so, so, so very much!
Well, I do miss Mommy a lot.
But I wanna stay with
my friends a bit longer.
What?!
Do you really like your friends
more than your own daddy?
[LION] The school
festival's coming up too.
I know!
You can invite everyone
over to our castle.
We'll make all sorts
of delicious treats.
I love food!
Gimme all those carbs and meat!
What? Stop this instant, Karen!
It's a castle with butlers
and luxe vacances.
Luxe vacances?
[KARIN] It wouldn't hurt to
take a little time off to relax.
Right?
Well, I suppose if
it's only for one week.
If my baby girl agrees,
you all could linger forever!
I'm gonna stay
here at the dorms.
I've got Foreigner
research to do.
[STRAFANSKY] There have been
multiple eyewitness reports
of what may be Foreigners
near our castle and gardens.
[LION gasps]
[MAHIRO]
Seriously?
Yes, a few years ago.
Many of my people saw
a beast that shone
with a divine light.
Yes, yes! Count me in!
Look at that.
[laughing]
I'll stay here.
[LION whining]
Only a monster could refuse
those big puppy dog eyes.
And that's why we're all here.
It's so hard to sleep like this.
I feel bad for taking time away
from all of your parents though.
I'm sure they were
so looking forward
to having their children
back at home with them.
Oh, you shouldn't
worry about that.
We're only here for a week.
It's true.
[YAYOI] Besides, all of us have
families who are occupied
with work.
They travel the world nonstop,
so we aren't able to see them
even when we do go home.
Family get-togethers
take a while
for us to plan since
we're all so busy.
[NINA]
Same goes for me.
Because my family is always
away on business as well.
[KARIN]
Oh, sorry about that.
She'll let go if you
tickle her armpits.
[NINA]
I see.
[KAREN laughing]
It must be the same
for Mahiro as well,
since she originally planned
to stay at the dorms for break.
Both my parents and
all my grandparents
are Foreigner researchers
for the ALCA,
so it's a family
tradition for us.
That explains a lot.
That's not a Foreigner, is it?
Nope, it's food.
[MAHIRO]
Hey, wait for me!
[MAHIRO] Anyway, since we were
just on the subject of family,
this might sound kinda
strange coming from me.
But my family is so
obsessed with their work
that our house in Pirari Town
is just being used
as a research lab while
they're out traveling
the world collecting
data and stuff.
Always gone.
I wonder when they're
ever coming home.
What's going on?
Why did you just stop walking?
Uh... Um, well...
Are you lonely?
No, not in the least bit!
See, we talk all the time.
That's awesome!
My daddy doesn't even
know how to use an emoji.
[BOTH laugh]
[STRAFANSKY sneezes]
That sneeze must mean
my beloved daughter
is talking about me--
In a good way!
Yes, of course
I'll have seconds.
Don't you ladies agree that
Lion's mother is beautiful?
Apparently, Linya used
to be a Logicalist too.
Exactly when did
you discover that fact?
Gathering information
is my specialty.
To pass down
that kind of legacy...
It must be amazing.
Gosh, I'm gonna melt
away if we stay in this heat
very much longer!
Let's go and find ourselves
something else to do!
Like what?
Something with meaning!
Studying or weight lifting.
Future Logicalists shouldn't
lay around sleeping all day.
We should constantly
be training!
[KARIN]
I agree,
but let's do that after the
air conditioner's been fixed.
[MAHIRO panting]
[yells]
Oh, wow.
Doesn't look like there
are any Foreigners.
Belle, can you sense
anything around here?
Well, they're not gonna let
us find them that easily.
Plus the Foreigner was witnessed
a pretty long time ago.
So there's a big probability
that it's already moved on.
A beast that shone
with a divine light.
Sounds like it might have
come from Monolium.
I was really hoping it'd
turn out to be Belle's father
or mother or some
kinda relative.
Her father?
[BELLE squeaks]
Honestly, I'd never really
thought about that before.
But it makes sense
that Belle would have
a mommy and daddy too.
Maybe.
But we don't actually
know much about
how Foreigners pass
along their genetic code.
[MAHIRO] We don't have
any idea if Foreigners
have a similar family
structure to us,
or really what kind of
lifestyle they have at all
on their planets.
And why's that?
ALCA hasn't shown much
interest in researching it.
They're too focused
on Trancing techniques.
[LION]
Oh, really?
Yeah, but have you
been able to figure out
anything about Belle?
Mm-hmm. I asked my mommy.
And she told me Belle
was her Covenanter
back when she was a Logicalist.
Who woulda guessed?
Anything else?
She said she'll tell me more
when I'm a little older.
Since the principal
gave you permission
to keep Belle with
you at all times,
I'm starting to wonder
if she has some type
of unique ability that you
don't know about yet.
[BELLE squeaks]
[MAHIRO] But now she
looks like a normal pet.
Oh, she's more than
just a pet to me.
Belle's like a cute furry
member of the family.
Isn't that right?
If you could somehow convince
Belle to Trance with you,
then you'd be able to see
what she really looks like.
What she really looks like?
[MAHIRO] She's in an
adaptive body right now.
Which means it's a
form that allows her
to adapt to our planet's Logic.
But back in Belle's home world,
she'd look completely
different than she does here.
Yeah?
Can you show me really quick?
[BELLE squeaks]
Looks like a "no."
That's too bad.
Someday, I would like to
go and visit Belle's world
so I can see her true form.
I mean, if she was
able to come here,
I'll bet that I could go there.
[BELLE squeaks]
[MAHIRO]
Uh...
Sorry, but we humans
don't have adaptive bodies.
So what does that mean?
[MAHIRO] Humans can't
travel to alternate worlds.
Not yet, at least.
[fireworks]
[LION chuckles]
It's a signal from Daddy!
I'm guessing he wants
us to head home.
[STRAFANSKY]
Fireworks!
[KAREN]
C'mon, sis!
Get in or you're gonna
miss out on all the fun!
Put down that book
and hop in the pool!
Yeah, yeah. Later, okay?
[KAREN]
Hooray!
Now this is what
I call a luxe vacance!
[KAREN laughing]
Karen!
Now, now.
It's quite shallow,
so jumping in like that
is dangerous.
Yay! Play time with my mistress!
I'm suffocating!
Oh, my gosh!
Your swimsuit is so cute!
Put me down right--
And she acts like such a child!
[KARIN]
Hey, mistress!
Do your best.
At what? I'm just
trying to go swimming!
And Karen, how long do you
plan on holding me up here?
Wait! Don't throw me!
[LION, MAHIRO laugh]
[MAHIRO]
We're back, guys!
[LION]
Wow! A swimming pool!
[BELLE squeaks]
You're home. Good.
I'm jumping in right now!
No!
My precious little princess
does not engage
in skinny dipping.
Okay.
[YAYOI]
Hey, Mahiro.
Did you locate your Foreigner?
[MAHIRO]
Naw, the trip was a bust.
You must be quite disappointed.
Yeah. But the forest
was really beautiful.
In my imagination,
Monolium looks kinda like
the spot we explored.
I would like to see
that for myself one day.
Then you should come
along with us next time.
[YAYOI chuckles]
[GIRLS gasp, laugh]
--[LION] Woo!
--[GIRLS laugh]
Lion.
I'm very happy that you've
made so many new friends!
My heart is somehow
both sad and filled with joy!
[LINYA]
How's it going?
[STRAFANSKY]
Hey, honey.
Everything's great here.
And the barbecue should
be starting on time.
I know that the
castle's air conditioner
isn't working right now,
but building your daughter
a pool in half a day
is still a bit excessive.
It was far easier
than building a country.
You're a good father.
Well, I'm also
a devoted husband.
Oh, dear.
What's the matter, Belle?
[BELLE squeaks]
Thank you so much
for everything.
I'm happy that you're
always watching over Lion.
Honey bear.
Aren't you glad that we
sent her to the academy now?
[LION laughs]
Yes.
But aside from her practical,
she's been getting straight Bs
and I think she can
do better than that.
Well, that's fine with me.
In fact I'm really
quite proud of her.
Aww.
[MAHIRO]
I'll take that one!
[GIRLS chattering]
[LION]
It's so good!
[KAREN]
A shooting star!
I wish I had something
really good to eat!
Oh, it's gone.
But you're already
eating good food, Karen.
Now that you mention it,
I heard on the news
that there's supposed
to be a big meteor shower.
Right.
And Liones is supposed to
be the best spot to see it,
latitude-wise.
Oh. Were you sleeping all
day because you stayed up
late last night?
[NINA] I was stargazing
until early this morning.
But apparently the shower
will be at its peak tonight.
I'd like to stay up late and see
the shooting stars this evening.
Do you know of an
ideal viewing spot?
On top of the castle
would be pretty good.
But stargazing is
best suited for an area
with very few artificial lights.
Then we know the
best place to go!
And it's not far at all.
[YAYOI] This doesn't feel
like "not far at all."
[KARIN]
Ugh! A centipede!
[KAREN]
Ah! It's a ghost!
[GIRLS scream]
[MAHIRO]
Wait a minute.
This isn't the same place
we went earlier, right?
[LION]
Don't worry about it.
[MAHIRO]
Are we going somewhere new?
That's exciting!
[LION]
So Nina.
You must like stars a lot.
Yes, I do.
I suppose that if I
hadn't been a Logicalist,
I probably would've
pursued astronomy.
[LION]
Do you wanna go visit that star?
[NINA]
Vega?
Yeah.
First off, there's
a big difference
between an astronomer
and an astronaut.
And secondly, Vega is
over 25 lightyears
away from this planet.
That said,
I would like to go someday.
[BELLE squeaks]
With this many shooting stars,
you can wish for
anything you want.
--[KAREN] Yummy food!
--[KARIN] Money! Money! Money!
Don't ask for too much.
[MAHIRO]
I want...
I want to go to another world.
I wanna go to another world!
I'm glad I got that out.
[MAHIRO] I always thought
it was really strange
that all these Foreigners
could come to Septpia,
but nobody had a clue
about how they normally
lived their lives back
on their own worlds.
No matter how many
science books I read,
or how much I asked my parents,
I couldn't figure it out.
So as soon as I formed
my own covenant,
I asked my Foreigner
partner about it.
But she didn't really
give me any answers.
Don't forget those
kinds of things
can sometimes be difficult
to communicate clearly.
I know.
And that's why
I need to go there
and see everything
with my own eyes.
When I told my parents
what I wanted to do,
they got really upset with me.
Oh? Why is that?
As far as we know,
humans don't have
adaptive bodies.
So going there would
put my life in danger.
But, I've heard there
were some people
who stepped up to
the challenge in the past.
There's just not much
information about them.
It's out there somewhere,
but it could be hidden
away in ALCA
top secret files.
Well...
I've decided not to
worry my folks right now.
Although, the bulk of
the research I'm doing
does revolve around that
specific area of interest.
So that's what you've
been up to. Hey, Belle.
Can you tell us something
about other worlds?
Guess not.
[BELLE singing]
Am I crazy, or is
Belle singing right now?
Well, I sing this song a lot,
so she probably picked
it up from me.
Can you sing it for us?
Um, it goes like this.
♪ What is this new
wondrous place? ♪
♪ So full of Logic
that intrigues. ♪
I've never heard
this melody before.
[STRAFANSKY]
Of course not.
After all, this song doesn't
come from Septpia.
Daddy!
I brought some sleeping bags.
Let's camp out under
the stars tonight!
Yay! [laughs]
Wait!
If that song isn't from Septpia,
then where did it come from
and how do you know
all of the lyrics?
Who knows?
According to Lion's mother,
it's a song that Rosa
used to sing quite a bit.
Which means it must
be a song from Monolium!
Let's find out if
that's true or not!
Okay, Lion.
Whip out your Card!
I left it at school like
the teachers told me to.
[YAYOI]
Now, Mahiro.
You know that students
aren't allowed to Trance
outside of school grounds.
No! But I'm so curious!
Totally and completely curious!
Hey, let's go back to
the dorm right now!
I'm fine with that.
Oh, no!
Nyet!
[STRAFANSKY crying]
[YAYOI]
Thank you for having us.
Now be careful on your way home.
I wish you'd all
stay a little longer.
We'll see each other
again pretty soon.
[LION whining]
Did I not mention that
I plan on going back
to the dorms early?
We shall be there too.
I have to organize the
school festival, after all.
[KARIN, KAREN]
Mm-hmm.
First off, I must come
up with a proper theme.
Oh, I think I know something
that'd work for us.
You do? What is it?
I'd like to hear
this idea of yours.
Well, it just came to me.
So I need to think
it over a bit more.
Bye-bye!
I'll see you soon!
Now, Lion.
What should we do?
How 'bout fishing in the ocean?
Or maybe a walk
up in the mountains?
I don't know which to
choose; it all sounds fun.
No matter what you
end up choosing...
...you'll do homework first!
[STRAFANSKY] It really
is great with Lion around.
Even drinks taste
more delicious!
I know.
Linya, you should
join me for a cocktail.
[LINYA] You still like me
even though I'm not young?
Was that mixer you had fun?
[STRAFANSKY]
Agh...!
[LINYA]
Here's a nice card.
"To The Silver Grizzly.
Thank you for inviting me
to that mixer the other day.
Next time, I'd like to see
some younger ladies."
He would? Really?
[STRAFANSKY]
That "Lightning of Kremlin!"
He knows how a battle
on the war front will go,
so why can't he
figure out the one
on the home front?
That's why the man can't
find a woman to marry him!
Those guys, am I right?
Always such a handful.
[laughs]
Yeah.
[STRAFANSKY]
I can explain this.
I heard from Lion's
teachers that some of them
were tired of being single.
So I organized a
little mixer for them.
I promise I was nothing
more than logistical support!
Please don't look
at me like that!
You've been the only
one I've thought about
since the day we met!
You're the most beautiful
and strongest woman
I've ever known.
I swear that I'll never have
eyes for anyone else
as long as I live!
[LINYA] It's not like I'm
really jealous or anything.
[STRAFANSKY]
That's good.