Hello, Class S.
I hope you lovely maidens
are having a good morning.
Your favorite student
council president here.
Are you surprised?
Since exams are
so incredibly boring,
I wanted to get
you fired up for--
Final exams are given in
both the summer and winter.
Class S students are
also required to take
a practical exam that tests
their Logicalist aptitude.
And these results will
impact your career options
in the future.
So it's really important
that you listen carefully
and prepare for this test.
Now, then,
here's your principal.
Wasn't that the girl...
...from Pirari town?
[BELLE squeaks]
This year, for our very
first Class S practical exam,
we have invited several
active-duty Logicalists
to be special guest examiners.
Chloe Maxwell.
Mana Asuha.
Yukari Nanahoshi.
Watch closely during this test
and learn from their teamwork.
You will need to use
your collective skills
as Logicalists to pass.
Details will be
released on the day of--
[MIZUKI]
Vice Principal!
You're forgetting an extremely
important bit of information!
What? What'd I forget?
Everyone should remember to
wear their school swimsuit
under their gym uniform.
I repeat--
[YAYOI]
Question!
Just let me say this
before you ask questions.
Everything you heard in
that announcement is true.
Exam details will
be revealed the day of.
So we really do need
to wear our swimsuits?
[LION]
Miss Fujisaki!
How are we supposed to prepare
if the exam is a secret?
[RINO] You personally
should look at Japanese,
mathematics, sociology, science.
[RINO chuckles]
I'm sorry.
You meant for the practical.
The only way for you to
become a strong Logicalist
is to study everything.
Everything?
Yes. If you only focus
on your physical strength,
you'll find yourself
off-balance.
You need to train your
heart and mind as well.
Oh. Okay.
[YAYOI] I made sure to spend
every moment of my spare time
studying for the written exam.
But I can't prepare myself
for the practical test
if I don't know what to expect.
[KARIN]
So, let's fix that.
Hey, Nina!
Do you know much
about the Logicalists
who'll be examining us?
I do.
They're very capable people.
Of course they are.
Do you think we have a
chance of beating them?
They said it's going to use
all of our collective skills.
So I don't think it's gonna
be just a mock battle.
Well then.
I guess the best thing for
me to do is train more
so I can up my
grasp on the basics.
Don't worry, mistress,
you'll be just fine.
No matter what the subject
or which opponent
you have to take on, you
always rise to the occasion.
Uh-huh. We'll be fighting
right by your side!
[YAYOI]
Karin. Karen.
That's really nice to hear.
But exams exist to test
an individual's strengths.
[KAREN]
Aww...
[KARIN]
If we're sneaky--
You mustn't.
We'll all do our best,
fair and square.
--[KARIN] Got it!
--[KAREN] Okay!
Our first practical
exam as first-years!
And the student who'll come
in first place will be me,
Yayoi Tachibana!
[YAYOI]
All right!
Now it's time to get
started with our training.
[KARIN]
My mistress.
I can't eat anymore.
I'm proud of how hard
you've been working.
Thank you, mistress.
Do your best today.
[YAYOI]
I swear to both of you
that I'll definitely
take first place.
I'll make you proud
and prove that I'm worthy
of being your mistress.
Morning, Nina.
Do you mind if I jog with you?
Good morning.
[YAYOI]
I must go faster!
Nina! You're running quite fast!
[NINA]
This is nothing.
[YAYOI]
Is that so?
I've noticed that lately, uh...
You've been...
...having mock battles and
Trancing after school hours.
And so have you, right?
Well, I just want to train
as much as possible.
[NINA]
Me too.
We take our written exam today,
so I had only planned on
working up a light sweat
this morning.
We may have just tied this race,
but I'll beat you
next time for sure.
You really must hate losing.
I won't deny that,
but I'm certain that I have
yet to reach my full potential.
And I still intend to place
first in the practical exam.
I may have been an active
duty Logicalist before this,
but my natural aptitude
is about the same as all
the other Class S students.
Maybe so, but you're still
hoping to come in first,
aren't you?
Of course.
But when it comes
to the practical exam,
there are several tough
opponents to beat.
Like Lion?
[NINA]
Certainly. And there's you.
[RINO] So everyone from
class is here, right?
We're not missing
anybody, are we?
[GIRLS]
We're here!
Okay. It's time for me
to explain the practical.
The exam rules are
pretty straightforward
since it's an obstacle course.
You must hit three checkpoints.
The academy entrance bridge,
the tall, sheer cliff,
and the passageway.
Once you get past
these obstacles,
you'll reach the goal
at the principal's office.
More importantly...
Protect these survivors.
[STUDENT 5A]
So many stuffed animals!
--[LION] Aww!
--[STUDENT 5B] They're adorable!
[RINO] Your mission
is to safely deliver
these innocent bystanders
to the finish line.
If your friend becomes injured,
or you're incapacitated,
you will be disqualified.
You're not allowed to hurt
your fellow classmates,
but other than that,
you're free to use
your powers
however you like.
Finally, you're only
allowed to Trance twice
during the exam.
Also, each Trance may only
last up to three minutes.
It would be very foolish
to Trance early on
since we don't know
what trouble may lie
ahead of us.
[RINO] The exam will be scored
from a total of ten points.
Those will be awarded for speed
and how you conduct
yourself in the field.
Now then, are you
ladies ready to start?
--[GIRLS] Yes!
--[BELLE squeaks]
Here we go!
[LION]
Bang!
[GIRLS]
Best of luck, everyone!
[LION]
It's Miss Kagura.
[STUDENT 5A]
And she's...
[STUDENT 5B]
Do we fight her?
[STUDENT 5C]
Don't ask me.
No way!
[STUDENTS]
Oh, no!
[LION]
Yay!
Okay then.
We'll dive down after you!
Off they go!
[KAREN]
Strip time!
[GIRLS squeal]
Swim, swim, fishy, fishy.
[KARIN]
Coming through!
They say the early bird
always gets the worm.
[KAGURA] Guess I should have
known no one would fight me.
[KAGURA]
But I'll slow them down.
[GIRLS screaming]
At this rate, we'll be
the first ones to the goal,
Kero-beros!
[LION]
Look at Karin.
She's already climbed
so high up.
They're moving
faster than I expected.
[KARIN yelling]
[KARIN]
Kero-beros, no!
[KERO-BEROS]
Farewell, my friend.
[MANA]
That makes one down.
[STUDENT 5G yells]
[GIRLS]
Ugh!
[STUDENT 5H]
What is this nasty stuff?
Just a bit more.
This is a big problem.
Time to get serious!
Ha ha!
There's more where
that came from! Ha!
Wait for me!
I'm gonna come up with you!
Trance!
Huh?
[YUKARI]
I'm behind you, Mana!
[coughs]
How about we move
to the next point?
[LION grunts]
[LION]
I made it!
I better move fast
or she'll beat me.
[YAYOI]
Oh, dear! No way!
[LION]
Are you okay?
Thank you, Lion.
I'm happy that my vines
got to you in time.
You really would've
hurt yourself falling
from this high up.
We're in a race--
why did you save me?
Heh. I saw you
were in danger,
so I just moved
without thinking.
What are you doing?
I must forfeit this
competition now.
How come?
Because it's against the
exam rules to borrow strength
from another.
[LION]
No it's not.
What do you mean?
Isn't the goal of
this whole test
to take our stuffed
animal friends safely
to the finish line?
Your mission is
to safely deliver
these innocent bystanders
to the finish line.
You're all free to use
your powers however you like.
Yes, you're right.
My judgment was clouded by a
profound misunderstanding.
Is this okay?
[KAGURA]
It's fine.
They haven't broken
any of the rules.
Who do we have left?
Looks like Mahiro and Karen
have been knocked out.
Next, we have Nina.
Let us make our sound in
the gaps between the waves.
You're as good as I remember.
Same goes for you, Chloe.
[CHLOE]
Ha!
Logic Drive!
Last Final Finish Sword!
[NINA grunts]
That trick's not
gonna work on me!
[NINA grunts]
Hey, that arrow almost
took out my eye.
I can--
Was that meant
to be a warning shot?
[MANA]
Perhaps it was.
Don't hold back on me.
Logic Drive!
--[CHLOE] Oh, crap!
--[MANA] We should move.
Yep. Moving!
[CHLOE yells]
Did that work?
[CHLOE] It doesn't seem fair
that you still get knocked out
even though you beat me.
It's fine. I failed the mission.
[YAYOI]
Ready?
I believe it's my
turn to go now.
Gate access!
Disfia!
Let's take them down, Qipao!
[QIPAO]
They look pretty tough.
But, I think we can
put up a good fight.
My name is Yayoi Tachibana!
The woman who will one day
stand as the top Logicalist!
I dig it.
It's nice to meet you.
I'm Chloe Maxwell.
Now come at me!
Stay back, you two.
I don't want you butting in.
[MANA]
Are you sure?
[CHLOE]
I'm sure!
[MANA]
Fine then.
All right. It's go time!
[CHLOE grunting]
[CHLOE yells]
[CHLOE grunts]
Isn't that...?
[CHLOE, YAYOI yell]
[CHLOE]
You won't catch me from behind!
Hang on!
Logic Drive!
Here comes Last
Final Finish Sword!
I guess I should've mentioned
that I'm mistress of two ninjas.
Wha--?!
You've gotta be kidding me!
Yayoi!
[CHLOE]
When did that happen?
At the beginning.
They set their plan in motion
once you started fighting.
Mana and I watched
that girl position herself
under the bridge.
[MANA]
Are you sure?
[CHLOE]
I'm sure!
[MANA]
Fine then.
Why didn't you guys
say something to me?
Sorry!
You told us not to
interfere, remember?
Tuna's safe.
Here's Yan-Yan.
Bienvenue.
[RINO]
Busy grading.
[LION]
I really got first place?
[laughs]
Congratulations!
[RINO]
You sure gave it your all.
You get a gold star.
[BELLE squeaks]
Hey, that tickles!
[GIRLS laughing]
[KAGURA] Why did you let Lion
cross the bridge before you?
[YAYOI] Because our goal was to
deliver the survivors to safety.
And Lion was the one
who remembered that fact.
[KAGURA] One day, you'll make
a good commanding officer.
Yes, of course I will.
After all, I'm the
future chief of ALCA.
[YUKARI]
Ah! The water here feels great!
All my pains are gone.
But I really wanted
to try fighting you too.
Who, me?
[CHLOE]
I saw your moves out there.
You're good at
fighting, aren't you?
I dunno...
And with Rosa's abilities,
I bet you're good
at supporting too.
Yeah.
Plus that plan
of yours was smart.
That's so nice,
but Yayoi's the one
who came up with the
winning plan, not me.
Yayoi's an awesome person.
She's super smart
and so reliable.
On top of that, she wakes
me up every morning.
Class representative, and, um...
Oh! And she wears
cute panda panties!
[YAYOI] That last point has
nothing to do with anything!
[GIRLS laughing]
But yeah, the only reason
I came in first place
was because of
Yayoi's big brain.
Come now, Lion.
I appreciate the compliments,
but you really need
to start recognizing
your own strengths.
--[LION] Huh?
--Look.
You should know that
I see you as a rival
that I will one day defeat.
You have a problem with that?
I'd rather just be friends.
I consider you a
friend and a rival.
That makes me happy!
[GIRLS laughing]
[LION]
A school festival?
[MAHIRO] Apparently, we open the
school up to the general public
so they can expand
their understanding
of both Logicalists
and Foreigners.
Oh.
[KAGURA]
Lion.
What now?
Keep holding the
mirror close to you.
Now close your eyes.
Can you describe how
it feels when you Trance
with Rosa?
[LION]
Like I'm calling out to her.
[KAGURA]
Okay. Imagine that feeling.
That's what I thought.
Open your eyes.
Oh, no.
Why's it all green now?
[KAGURA] This mirror's
purpose is to reveal
the inner heart
balance of the user.
Let me explain then.
A Trance is a state of
being where a Logicalist
and Foreigner each
share half their Logic.
Allowing them to become one.
In your case,
you empathize strongly with
the Foreigner's feelings,
giving away too much of
your Logic to that partner.
The green shows Monolium.
Which means...
You're reflecting how much
you entrust yourself to Rosa.
Is this bad?
Lion.
I wanted you to know that
you're in a dangerous position.
If you can't learn
to retain your own will,
it's very possible that
you could damage
both yourself and
your surroundings.
Nina!
[NINA]
Oh, Lion.
What brings you here?
Um, well...
Let's see.
Just stuff.
Are you heading back to
the dormitory now too?
I am! Let's walk together.
[LION]
I wonder what's for dinner.
I hope it's tuna.
That'd be nice.
[KOZUE]
Why do I even bother?
I knew that's how it'd go.
I was positive the group
date wouldn't turn out well.
And guess what?
I was right, as usual.
[RINO]
Yeah, it went south really fast.
[KAGURA] Are you talking
about that mixer?
[RINO]
It was a disaster!
They were all so fit,
but very weak.
--[KAGURA] What?
--[KOZUE] Exactly.
Honestly, I can't stand a guy
who's weaker than me.
[KAGURA]
What do you expect?
A normal human could never
be stronger than us, right?
[KOZUE] That's why I
prefer a smart gentleman!
Now's the era of hot guys.
But I want a really tall
one who makes lots of money!
You've sure got some high hopes.
[RINO]
But me,
I just wish I could find
someone like you.