Say goodbye to your
precious little Johnny.
Your luck ran out the moment
I saw you in the alley.
Hello? Whoever this is,
I'm kind of busy at the moment.
Have it your way.
Let's take a break...
And while you're waiting
here for me to return...
I want you to feel nice
and ashamed of yourself.
Well, here we are.
Thank you.
You know if you wanted
to stay longer I wouldn't mind.
I'll just meet up
with you later.
Sounds good...
And remember to bring along
your friends when you do...
I'll see you then.
Hello? Morimi residence.
Saki...? Hurry back home, now.
I'm sorry, but
I can't face Ryosuke;
I'm too ashamed.
Saki, don't be silly.
He's not angry with you.
Well... I just don't
wanna come home.
Why are you
talking like this...?
Tell me where you are,
I can come get you.
I'm at Micchon's...
I'm gonna stay here a while,
so please don't worry about me.
That's unacceptable.
I demand you come home!
Sorry, Asako.
I'll call you later.
I wouldn't worry about it.
It's not like we don't
know where she is...
Why don't we just let
her do her thing for now?
Honey, you are just
way too easy on her.
I better apologize
to Osugi, too.
Hey... What're you
doing down there?
Can you... lend me some clothes?
I know, my story sounds fishy.
But it's the truth.
It doesn't sound fishy,
it sounds preposterous!
I think you need to go
home and get some rest...
And sorry... but it seems
to me like this Takizawa guy
is trying to pull the
wool over your eyes.
And what are you wearing?
Doesn't seem like your style.
What's the big deal...?
Saki looks good in
everything she wears...
And I think this Takizawa
story's interesting.
We'd be fools not to pursue it.
Really?
I agree, the whole
ordeal sounds absurd...
but our discussion
needs to go beyond
telling Saki whether
or not she should
move in with him.
With the way things
have been going lately,
the future of our
little club is in danger.
She's right.
I don't believe this.
How did my PR girl get
wrapped up in this mess...?
And now the staff
is supporting you...
All for some shady character
who's probably
trying to find a way
to take advantage of everyone.
I don't know what happened
to you on your trip...
but you have changed
since you've gotten back.
What happened to the girl
who would shrug off
Osugi's desperate come-ons
like a devout nun...?
Despite all of his
constant groveling...
Not to mention the
thousands of other Johnnies
over the last four years,
all hyped up on testosterone
and willing to do
anything to have you...
Now at what point did you
become so weak in the knees?
No, it's... heh...
Testosterone aside...
Let us not forget it was
you who said, and I quote...
"Come hell or high-water,
Saki must be a part of
this business venture."
It's true...
Remember the only
reason Eden works
so efficiently is
because Saki makes up
for one of your
major weaknesses.
You're good at a lot of things,
Hirasawa, but you're
not a natural leader.
What, and he is...?
Look, I don't have any problems
with you pointing
out my faults...
but don't you think
there's a huge discrepancy
between myself and well...
everything this Takizawa
person stands for?
Sure, I did postpone my
graduation for a while...
but I'm gonna use that time
to continue advancing
the business model...
Meanwhile, Takizawa shows up...
with no clothes,
no memory, no job,
no idea who his family is,
or even his favorite movie!
Seriously...
Why would you trust
someone like him...
The guy's got nothing!
Oh that poor, poor boy.
What that must've been like:
All alone and lost,
with nothing but his gun waving
around in the cold breeze...
Can we please
stay on topic here?!
Excuse me.
Hirasawa...
I've been listening to
you guys this whole time...
and from everything
I've heard so far...
You've made Takizawa out to
be a worthless troublemaker
and I don't think
that's the case.
He seems to treat
Saki with respect,
and more than anything,
he's a go-getter
who isn't afraid of
getting his hands dirty.
The guy lives in
a shopping mall,
so he must be loaded... also...
he owns a dog,
so how bad can he be?
Who asked you?!
Sorry.
Sitting here and talking
about him isn't helping...
Let's just go and meet him...
find out ourselves.
I agree...
There's no better way
than a first impression...
Plus, then we can size him up.
I think that's a good point,
but just to be on
the safe side...
let's not walk right in.
First, let's do a little...
snooping around.
Whatever you say...
Mister Top-Secret Agent.
I'm just exercising
some caution...
Well, what do you think, Saki?
I'm fine with that...
Better safe than sorry...
I've always been a little wary
of the things Takizawa told me,
because of how
crazy they sound...
and if they're true,
it's scary stuff...
That's why... we should
all go together.
Alright...
I'll go and get us a car...
We head out in
thirty minutes, people.
Hirasawa.
I need to get something
off my chest about Osugi...
Last night he took me to a
really expensive restaurant
with champagne and everything...
It didn't occur
to me at the time,
but after hearing Saki's
story, it dawned on me...
He'd originally planned
that dinner to be for her.
Seriously?
Why didn't you tell me
about this earlier?!
Because, I didn't want
to say anything
in front of her...!
You see... Osugi got pretty
hammered during dinner...
which leads me
to believe he saw Saki
with Takizawa
earlier in the day.
It probably broke his heart.
So... What'd he do afterwards?
He started walking home,
completely drunk
out of his mind...
And now, apparently,
even Saki can't get
in touch with him...
What should we do...?
We're on the verge of
making a momentous decision
on the future of this company...
We can't just leave
him out in the cold!
I agree.
Even though he did
get a job elsewhere...
he will always be a
valuable founding member...
Additionally, this would
be a golden opportunity
for us to keep Saki
from leaving Eden...
Alright, find Osugi and
put him in the club room
until we all get back.
Right. You got it.
This is where he lives?
Are there any other ways in?
I think if there were,
the homeless would have
found their way in by now.
We could be walking
straight into a trap...
No turning back now.
Saki, you could be marrying
into some serious
money with this guy!
Maybe he bought it cheap.
Property values in this area
took a nosedive
after Careless Monday.
But for all we know,
he could've paid top dollar
for the place before
the missile strike.
Holy crap - Come look at this!
This mall is heaven on earth!
Look at this shirt!
It's so cute! I have to have it!
Careful, girls.
You're gonna get us in trouble.
Whatever, "Dad"!
Looks like he's home.
He lives upstairs in the
movie theater's VIP room.
Hello?
Aren't you going to be our brave
and fearless leader and
introduce him to the team?
'Scuse me!
What's wrong?
Was he not up there?
No, he wasn't...!
But he's got this place covered
in surveillance cameras!
He's probably been
watching us the whole time!
We need to get out of
here before he finds us...!
The guy's obviously dirty!
We don't need to get
involved with someone like him!
Wait a minute. Who's dirty?
Isn't it obvious?
I'm talking about Takizawa!
Hey.
Welcome to my home...
glad to have you.
Oh, look...!
The little guy has wings!
I don't think I've ever
seen anything so cute!
Well as far as I can tell,
this title is legit.
I just dug it out of
a filing cabinet today.
Okay I think I'm following
you for the most part...
But what I still don't
get is why you decided
to financially
support our business...
And before you answer that,
I'd like to know your
intentions with Saki.
My intentions
are good-natured...
I just felt there was
no need for her to work
for elitist men
who'd have the nerve
to dump their lunch in
her lap to prove a point.
If everyone in Japan...
and not just Saki,
turned into NEET's,
we could flip this
country around...
The old farts who take
their power for granted
would have no other choice
but to bow before
us in gratitude.
You know, that is not a
very well thought out plan.
How so...?
You guys basically
had the same idea only
with some subtle differences...
I had a chance to play
with Eden of the East...
It's very well done...
A visual search engine
that uses social networking.
Brilliant.
I even tried to trip up the
system by using it on my dog.
But no matter what angle I used,
it was able to
recognize him every time.
Micchon here is the one
who wrote all the
code for the program.
No kidding...?
Hey, you're pretty
talented there, Mittan.
She has a sharp tongue
when she's around
people she knows,
but always tends to
clam up around strangers.
Even when she was a little kid,
she only wanted to play
with her cousin, Hirasawa.
Aw, she's adorable.
My name's not Mittan.
So if you register
something on the site...
any cell phone
can access the data?
That's pretty cool... Genius...
I was talking to Saki...
We were discussing how
great the program is
and about all the
potential for monetization
if it were released...
Why haven't you
explored that yet?
Explain the point of
having assistants...
if I have to do it myself.
We're terribly sorry.
The road ahead is a long one...
In more ways than one.
Juiz?
How may I be of service?
I am in desperate
need of a secretary
fluent in both
French and Cantonese.
And I need it right now.
Order received...
Noblesse oblige...
I pray that you, one of
the most industrious CEOs
in the world, continue
your service as a savior.
You in the glasses...
Consider yourself laid off.
I don't believe this.
I didn't do anything!
To make a long story short,
we ran into some trouble
that happens all the time
on websites and message boards,
though I'm not really at liberty
to discuss any of
the finer details.
In the end,
it got pretty nasty...
a girl was forced to drop out...
and the university opened
an investigation on us.
Ooh... what about this?
No?
You're crazy.
Well, I think it's cute...
Suit yourself.
We started out as a
small-time recycling group
focused on awareness...
but thanks to the
development of Eden,
we soon realized that
items that were seen
as junk had real intrinsic
value to some people.
We owe everything to
Saki for not only seeing
the potential in the program,
but for also
getting the word out.
It didn't take long
for the other members
to jump on board,
and before we knew it,
the entire student body...
was obsessively using
the technology...
Eventually, people
realized Eden could be used
as a highly accurate
match-making service.
And is that where all
the trouble stemmed from?
Yeah...
Everything started
to snowball after that.
One member of our group
left to pursue a job,
and now Saki has
decided to leave home
for some unknown reason,
which she refuses
to discuss with us...
I'm ashamed I let things
get so out of control.
Let's go... It's time to leave.
What's up...?
Could you and Takky not come
to an agreement on a deal?
I am a NEET, understand...?
I've always prided
myself on that.
I don't have a
specialized skill set,
like Micchon or Saki,
which is why I studied
management and law.
I chose this so
I could support the
elite NEETs and
eventually become one.
I think you're already there.
Almost, but I'm not there yet.
What does this have
to do with the deal?
Eden of the East is
a NEET's paradise...
I don't want to solicit
help from an outsider.
Think of it as the jealousy...
all of the 'have-not's'
feel... towards the 'haves'.
Whatever you say...
I understand...
Actually, I don't.
Excuse me?!
I understand getting
involved with someone
who has amnesia takes
a leap of faith,
but you have to trust me...
In reality, I'm the
one asking for your help.
Now then...
I can't explain the
details of my situation...
but will you help me carry out
my noble obligations
as one of the 'haves'?
You can take my offer
for funding as a
show of my gratitude.
Do it, Hirasawa. Please...
I'm behind this
one hundred percent.
I wanna join Eden full time
and help you run it.
Sounds like a
perfect opportunity...
It was Saki's lack
of involvement
that troubled you the most...
What's there to lose?
You've gotta be kidding me.
I'm saved by Saki again?
In the end, does it matter
who saves who...?
Let's make a difference...
moving forward,
working together.
I just want to make
it clear to everyone
that I still don't
completely trust you.
Though I do trust you
enough to shake your hand...
That's a start... But...
when it comes to Eden,
I still call the shots. Agreed?
That's fine...
Now let's get to work
on a NEET's paradise.
Yeah!
Now we're one, big happy family!
Thanks, Takizawa... Really...
You're not
only helping me out,
you're helping out
the whole group.
No need...
I really admire
people like Hirasawa
who go out of their way
to help their fellow man.
Do you... mind if
I ask you a question?
What did...
What did you mean
when you told me
to come over to your place...?
I mean, I don't
think I had told you
about Eden of the
East yet, right?
You wanna know?
You needed a
change of clothes...
I think you'd look
really pretty in yellow.
Look at Micchon.
I can't believe how quickly
she's warmed up to him.
It's not like her.
I can't tell if
they're playing together
or if he's just
messing with her head.
You really have to pack
it in there firmly,
otherwise it'll
just topple over...
See, Mittan?
It's hard for me,
I'm not as strong as you...
And my name's not Mittan.
Hey...! Come on out,
we're ready for ya!
What've you guys been up to?!
Okay, it's show time!
I didn't know you were
such a scaredy-cat, Mittan!
Micchon... not Mittan.
Hello...? Oh, hey Kasuga...
Have any luck finding Osugi?
Uh... yes... and no...
if that makes sense.
No, it doesn't. What's up?
Well... The thing
is it's possible...
that Osugi's been abducted by
that psycho, Johnny Hunter.
The Johnny Hunter?
The one and only.
I was doing some
digging around online...
and I happened across a series
of disturbing posts
on a message board.
And why were you
looking for him online?
That's not important.
This guy is claiming
to have been imprisoned
in a hotel room by
a suspicious woman,
and he keeps posting
picture messages
and begging for help.
He's been doing this for
the past eighteen hours.
From what I can tell,
the police haven't
gotten involved yet...
but it is causing
quite a stir online...
I've looked over these
posts hundreds of times,
Hirasawa, and I'm
convinced it's Osugi.
Send me the URL for
the message board.
Will do.
I also found some
unofficial estimates
that put the number of
Johnny Hunter victims
at twenty thousand,
so the idea that Osugi
is next in line is
not out of the question.
Understood.