Wait, so you're saying
Takizawa has a phone
that can do anything
he asks it to?
That's insane!
This line's too long!
Let's try somewhere else!
Anyway, before you
do anything else,
take a look at the
data that Panties sent...
I've tried calling him,
but he's not picking up.
I'll take a closer
look as soon as I can...
but whatever you do,
do not come to Toyosu!
Huh...? How come?
Well uh...
You know those twenty-thousand
missing NEETs...?
They're all in the movie theater
right now looking for Takizawa.
This place isn't safe anymore.
I'm impressed, Hirasawa.
How'd you find this spot?
I saw it in the
real estate documents.
So do you really
think we'll be all right
if we hide in here?
It's our only option.
We can't reason with a
bunch of angry, naked men.
Wow.
They seem more concerned
with finding their phones
than they do about
freezing to death.
I'm not surprised.
Their phones are
obviously important to them.
Hello?
Hey, it's me.
So we're gonna head
your way after all.
It'll be much faster to go
over all the data together.
Okay.
But are you absolutely
certain there will be
a sixty-missile
attack this time...?
And if so, is there
anything we can do ourselves
to stop it from happening...?
It's not like we have magical
phones at our disposal.
I don't think Takizawa
saved all those people
on Careless Monday because
he had a "magic" phone...
I think he did it because
that's what needed to be done.
Then what was the point of
erasing his memories...?
And it certainly doesn't explain
why all these NEETs
are so angry with him.
He's right, Saki!
They wouldn't be so pissed
if he hadn't done something
to make 'em that way!
Osugi...
Takizawa had to do more
than just protect people
from the missiles.
He also had to protect
the twenty-thousand NEETs
who helped with the evacuation.
To draw suspicion
away from them,
he set himself up to
look like the sole bad guy,
then wiped his memory.
After he got that phone and
learned about the attacks,
Takizawa used the Internet
to anonymously assemble
an army of volunteers,
and they evacuated people
from the landing
sites by methods
that were borderline criminal...
And you're saying the volunteers
were the twenty-thousand NEETs?
Yeah, I think so...
But after the missiles hit and
the initial shock wore off,
the people they'd rescued
started getting angry,
and venting to the media...
They wanted answers:
How did anyone know to evacuate
them in the first place?
Was there some ulterior
motive behind it all?
See, Takizawa's volunteers
didn't really know
for certain that the missiles
would come, so apparently,
some of them had
used the opportunity
to steal things at the sites.
Most of them, though,
were simply excited
and proud to have been part
of saving so many lives.
But they had to keep
their involvement a secret.
And when many of the people
who'd lost their homes
in the attacks remained
vocal about their suspicions
that they'd somehow
been deceived...
well, eventually, the NEETs
couldn't remain
silent any longer.
They began firing back at
the evacuees in forums
and message boards online...
and very quickly,
the different rumors
and conspiracy theories began
to spiral out of control...
So, to help diffuse
the situation,
Takizawa used a number of
aliases to gather the NEETs
at the mall in Toyosu,
and he redirected their anger
by telling them
he'd been the one
who orchestrated
the missile attacks.
That explains why they know him
by so many different names,
and why they're still
so openly angry with him...
That, and the fact that he
helped shipped them to Dubai
for three months to shield
them from the spotlight
until media interest
in the story died down...
Public opinion can be fickle.
And people are quick to latch
on to unfounded rumors...
Especially in times of crisis,
when all they really want
is someone to blame...
Takizawa was betrayed
by the people he'd gone
to such great lengths to
protect, so he lost hope...
And that's what led him
to erase his memories...
Has he remembered
all this himself?
I don't know...
What I do know is,
it's up to us this time.
We have to find a way
to stop these new
attacks from happening.
Dammit, why did you have to
get us involved in all this?!
Even if Takizawa is a
good person at heart...
it's obvious that the
guy is a complete idiot...
He has a phone
that can literally do
anything, and yet...
he still finds a way
to screw everything up!
I think the missile
target areas are listed
in the data Itazu
sent over to us...
If we use the Internet
like Takizawa did
for Careless Monday...
there's a chance we
may be able to stop it.
Yeah, good idea...
Nowadays, even the threat
of violence is enough
to get you arrested...
I'm sure that we'll get
some sort of reaction...
if we post another missile
attack is on the way...
But...
But what?
We can't post anything
to the Net right now.
What do you mean?
The laptop with
all the data on it...
has fallen into the
hands of the zombies!
I'm so sorry!
I must've left it on the
bar when we ran out of there!
Hey look...! I see it!
Where?
Right there. It's that guy!
But how are we supposed
to get it back from him?
I think I know...!
Our only chance is to hit
them with a stealth attack.
Which means we should
all take our clothes off!
Huh...? Wait, you
want us to strip?
Yes...! It makes
perfect sense...
The best place to hide a
tree is in the woods...
So to blend in with the NEETs,
we should all be naked!
Looks like they
haven't noticed us yet...
Guess my plan is working, huh?
It would appear so.
Let's go...!
Don't hesitate,
you have to commit!
Yeah... I guess you're right.
You have got to be kidding me!
I don't know how
we're gonna do it,
but we have to find the others.
I say we run as fast as we
can and hope for the best.
Girls!!
Nice laptop you got there.
Oh thanks...
but it's useless
without the password.
Let me take a shot at it.
Wait a sec...
You guys have hair.
And you're really pale.
Excuse me. Run!
Oh great, they're following us.
Don't worry.
They look like the type
who are only into
two-dimensional girls.
This way!
Get back here!
Osugi...! Catch!
Run Os...
Run...! Don't stop-Keep going!
Saki!
Osugi, why aren't you
wearing any clothes?
Don't let the computer touch it!
Geez, do you have any idea
what I went through
to get that back?
Sorry, but all that matters
right now is the data!
Come on...! Get in here!
Sis!
I'm so glad you two are okay!
Enough with the hugs,
let's get to work!
If I remember correctly,
we should be looking
for some red text.
Like this?
The Diet building
and Roppongi are listed!
All right, let's split this up.
First, send it to all
of our cell phones.
You got it.
Wait...! Oh no... Look at this!
Toyosu?
What the hell?
Test 1-2-3...
Just making sure
the camera's working.
It's Takizawa!
Can you believe this?
Hey, Johnnies...!
You may be wondering
why I've gathered
you here today.
Well, believe me,
it's for a good reason.
I'm minutes away
from launching yet
another missile attack to kill
each and every one of you.
I'm getting rid of everyone
who knows the truth
about Careless Monday
and teaching the rest
of the country a
lesson all in one shot.
That's a lie!
Why would you say
something like that...?
I know you're not capable
of committing mass murder...
Stop joking around
and tell the truth!
Believe me, this is not a joke.
But there is good news.
You still have a
chance to survive...
If any of you Johnnies
wanna live, head to the roof.
I'll meet ya there.
Takizawa.
Damn it! I can't believe
we let Juiz slip away!
Sorry kid, but from here on out
it's every man for himself...
I believe Mister Outside
is still alive after all
and I plan on locating him...
If I find anything
I'll contact you,
otherwise don't expect
to hear from me.
But...
I think you've been
played, my friend.
What do you mean?
I mean you're really stickin'
your neck out on this one...
What if he's the Supporter,
did you ever stop
to think of that?
He put you up to
launching another attack,
to eliminate the witnesses...
Well, what if he's just setting
you up for an epic failure
so he can take you
out of the game?
Best of luck to you, man...
But keep your eye out for
that clown Number Nine...
I'm pretty sure he's gonna
try to pull somethin' again.
It's too late!
He can't stop it.
Didn't you read the news?
They altered the strategic
programming protocols
for the Patriot missile
systems... Two days ago.
Save yourselves.
We'll find a way out
of here eventually.
That won't be easy...
All of the fire
exits are blocked.
You think we can make
it to the elevator?
Uh, hold on.
Hold that door.
Hold on, wait! Wait!
That was close!
Open up!
Hey! Come on, guys!
Wait for the next one!
Osugi!
It's him!
Takizawa?!
You must be Osugi.
You've got balls... and
I expected nothing less.
Takizawa, wait!
You didn't come here
to kill everyone.
You're here to
save 'em, right...?
You're gonna paint yourself
as the bad guy again...
to protect us!
So you listened in on
the phone all the way
to the end, huh?
Until my battery ran out, yeah.
Afterwards, I went
back to Itazu's place
and found out that he had sent
all the logs over to Hirasawa.
So...
I knew you guys
would eventually turn up
here once you saw the data.
Your memories... are they back?
Hey, guys...!
Good to see you again...!
The missiles should be
arriving any minute now!
This time around...
I want you to post
solutions for shooting down
the missiles onto the
Eden of the East website!
Look at 'em go!
Yeah.
Ah, the power of crowd-sourcing.
Put enough minds together
and you can achieve brilliance.
Just you watch.
I'm sure they'll come up
with something miraculous,
just like they did
on Careless Monday.
It's not like I did that
all by myself, you know.
Come on, guys!
Get hacking! What?
We're not hacking anything.
Juiz?
This is Juiz...
I've culled the information from
the posts on Eden of the East
and have narrowed them down
to the most effective ways
of countering the missiles...
I pray for your continuing
service as a Savior.
Thank you...
Let's get started then.
Bang!
Hey, you made it.
Is Takizawa the one who
called in the fighter jets?
Yep... but he could
never have done it
without the help
of all these NEETs.
This is amazing.
Is this happening
all over Japan?
Anytime you want
to come and save me,
I'll be waiting for you...
Selecao Number Nine.
Well would you
look at that... I did it.
He can shoot down all
the missiles he wants.
Doesn't change the fact
this country's at
the end of its rope.
It looks like he
made it just in time.
Bang!
Who am I, the
Sundance Kid...? Idiot...
Saki!
Hey, Juiz?
Yes?
I'm afraid this time
around passing myself off
as a terrorist won't be
enough to cover all my tracks.
So I'd like you to use
the rest of my balance
to make me the King of Japan.
Did you say... king?
That's right.
There are a lot of intelligent
people in this country,
but none of them are willing
to step up and lead the way.
Honestly...
I'd rather not be the guy
to have to do it, either...
But there's one girl
who truly believes in me.
Order accepted...
Noblesse oblige...
I pray you shall be a splendid
prince the next time we speak.
When that time comes...
I hope I'm the same as I am now.
Oh, Juiz! One more thing!
Damn it... Well isn't
that a shame...
No gold ring on
this merry-go-round.
And so he became a prince...
In this world without a King.