Juiz... It looks like
I've done it again.
Killed?
Yes... You know
where to find me.
It's the usual place.
I've pinpointed your location.
Room 1109.
Would you be a doll and
handle the cleanup for me...?
I really don't care
how you manage it,
as long as it's done
elegantly, understand?
Yes... Noblesse oblige...
I pray for your continuing
service as a savior.
I can hardly believe it...
I was already caught up
in this stupid game
before I wiped my memory.
If this Mister Outside
gave me the choice today
to sell my life
for ten billion yen,
then I'd say thanks,
but no thanks.
Damn it! I'm screwed!!!
Who does this Mister Outside
think he is anyway?!
The prick has a god complex!
Gimme a minute alone with him
and I'd bash in his fac--!
That was a close one...
If I throw this phone
away the Supporter
will sneak up
and slit my throat.
Wait, is that... Takizawa?
You dick!!!
Settle down.
I take it you're
not the Supporter?
It's your fault, asshole!
What the hell are
you talking about?
Don't play dumb with me...!
Do you have any idea what we had
to go through these
last two months...?
You promised to take us
to a consumer's paradise
and instead you dumped us
in the middle of a desert!
Then some jerk-off
foreman from India
started ragging on us
for being weak and useless.
He beat us. He spit on us.
We went days without food,
without money or even a
clue as to what was going on!
It was so humiliating!
Sorry, do I... know you?
Are you serious...?
You don't remember?
Ah, forget it.
It's meatbuns...
So, next month
I'm getting married
to a girl I met over there.
Of all the places in the
world you coulda sent us,
I still don't understand
why you chose Dubai...
but I guess it all
turned out okay for me now
that I can re-enter
society again.
Later.
What just happened?
Sorry to make you do this right
before your big interview...
It's just that you're so
much better at it than me.
No big deal.
I do it all the time.
I hope you don't mind,
but I decided to make
you into a cookie.
So I'm guessing they'll probably
be a little rough with
you in the interview...
Just try not to
be defensive, okay?
But... if you decide you
can't take anymore abuse,
don't feel like you
have to force yourself.
What do you mean?
If you need to take more time
to find the perfect job...
we're more than happy
to float you awhile.
I've already been enough
trouble to you as it is.
Come on, Saki, don't be silly...
You're our family.
That's easy for you to say.
Sometimes kindness
can really hurt.
Hey, Saki.
Good morning.
Hey, Osugi,
I didn't even see you.
I barely recognize
you in that suit.
Yeah, the whole corporate look
doesn't really fit me, does it?
Not really.
I feel like I haven't
seen you in forever...
Guess things've
been pretty crazy
since we came
back from our trip...
Did you hear the
news about Hirasawa?
He decided to defer his
graduation for a year...
And of course he
made this big decision
while we were all in Manhattan.
Oh, that...
Yeah, I figured something
like that was up
ever since he told us he
couldn't come with us...
Good call...
We've always dreamed
of turning Eden
into a real business,
so I understand...
He still wants to chase it...
Guess that's a
choice you can make
when your family's got money...
He says being a NEET's
all he's cut out for:
"No Employment,
Education, or Training."
But you and I both know
he's capable of more.
As long as he's
willing to try...
Did you know he's already
gotten six job offers?
Funny how he
leaves that part out.
I just hope he doesn't
wait too long...
I've seen guys pushing forty,
still living off their parents,
griping about how they could
never fit into society...
That's gonna be him one
day if he's not careful.
Heh, you know what I mean?
Yeah, I guess
everything you're saying
makes perfect sense, Osugi...
So, uh...
Do you have any free time
after your interview today?
Why do you ask?
Oh, well...
I was hoping you'd want
to get some dinner...
We could celebrate graduation
and both of us finding jobs...
I mean we're
already dressed up...
so we should hit
the town, right?
I should be done around two,
so I can pick you up
if you want?
Mhmm...
Yes!
Congratulations...
I'm sure your mission is clearer
now that you remember the rules.
Well technically I don't
remember anything...
This whole idea
of saving the nation.
Can the mission get
any more vague...?
I'm... starting to
question just how
feasible this idea really is.
Can you elaborate more?
What I mean is...
If you give twelve
random people a phone
with ten billion yen on it, and
tell 'em to change the world,
the chances of 'em
succeeding are slim...
Maybe the Prime Minister
could do it...
Right...?
Nah, you'd need to find someone
even bigger than him to
pull it off, for sure...
So--what kinda person
does that make me?
You think I can make the
Prime Minister cry uncle...?
Really?
You've got the life, pooch.
Order received.
Huh?
Noblesse oblige...
Please turn on the television...
I pray for your continuing
service as a savior.
Turn on the TV?
Based on these
current documents,
there is evidence that the
missiles used on Careless Monday
are identical to those
that were recently deployed
by the Maritime
Self-Defense Forces.
Now, sir...
Is it not true that
you were aware...
of not only the
missiles' existence,
but their use by the MSDF?
We've also received
intelligence suggesting
the terrorists behind
the attacks are part
of an organization calling
themselves Seleção.
The Prime Minister
has the floor.
Uncle.
What's he saying?
What? Speak up!
Uncle.
Come on Juiz,
that's not what I meant.
Okay so you proved your point...
You're powerful... huh...
What...? Crap, I forgot!
Saki sent me this message
yesterday and I never read it!
"I went home this morning...
did something happen to you...?
Hope your memories came back"...
Damn, I made her worry.
Takizawa...?
"Sorry I couldn't make
it to the late show...
My memories haven't
come back yet,
but I'm doing fine...
What are you doing right now?
We should meet up...
There's something that I've been
meaning to talk
to you about."...
Now's not a good time.
No reply.
She must be pissed at me...
I should go apologize in person.
Juiz...
Do you remember the girl
I was with yesterday...?
Yeah.
Did you see the
Diet hearings on TV?
Apparently just
saying the word "uncle"
shot the old man's approval
ratings up ten percent.
That only cost him sixty yen?
Juiz... It's me.
If any of you have dreams
of becoming a
professional model...
then you can forget it.
Trust me, you'll have
a much better chance
of winning the lottery.
Ah, if it isn't Number Nine...
He has really
changed his approach
since his return to the fray.
Did anyone watch
the Diet hearings?
Makes me wonder how Number One
will react to this nonsense.
There are realists and
there are romantics...
I have no intention
of taking either side.
I usually just
go with the cutest.
Oh, speaking of...
Do I have anything on
my plate for tonight?
Yes.
Well I'm starting
to get the urge
to perform one of my
disappearing acts again...
so you better keep
an eye on me, okay?
Ma'am?
I'm not very effective at
controlling myself these days.
You were lucky.
Having been a
survivor of that incident,
tell us in your own words how
you see this latest
terrorist attack...
We want your honest opinion,
so don't hold back.
Uh...
The youth of today almost seemed
to welcome Careless Monday
with open arms, did they not?
Well...
Up until now, there
were no casualties,
so such a brash opinion
was a viable stance
to take on the issue...
But all that changed
with the most recent attack
when people were
actually murdered...
I feel horrible
for the victims...
That's enough... Thank you.
Okay... Not what
I was hoping for...
You see...
I wanted an opinion
that was truly unique.
Something that doesn't just
regurgitate the status quo...
We need people who
can think outside the box.
I'm glad you made it through
the attack alive and well...
Where there is life,
there is hope, right?
Hey... I know it's a bit early,
but since you came
all the way out here,
what do you say we
do some lunch...?
Our cafeteria is
among the best in town.
Sure!
Where is he?
Maybe I went to
the wrong cafeteria?
Sorry about that.
No, don't worry about it...
It's no big deal.
Did you see that girl
wearing the ramen earlier?
Oh, I saw her.
It's been awhile since the boss
has had to pull out that trick.
Yeah, tell me about it...
You know, the boss may
be the bad guy here,
but really, could that girl
have been any more dense...?
If she'd actually gotten
a clue after sitting there
alone for nearly an
hour, she wouldn't be
totally soaked in
beef broth right now.
I know, the girl
needs a reality check.
Seriously--you
miss your interview
'cause you're on vacation, and
you still expect to get hired?
Not gonna happen, sister.
You'd have to be
pretty naïve to think
a few good connections
are all you need
to land a job these days.
I guess our customers
like her sense of humor...
maybe she could
find work in sales.
Hello. Sangetsu Bakery.
Yes...? Oh...!
I wanted to thank
you for arranging
that interview for my sister...!
Huh...? Oh, okay... Yes.
I see. Well...
I'll pass along the message...
We appreciate the opportunity...
Right... You have
a good day, too.
Hey, Saki.
I'm glad I caught you.
I wanted to apologize for
what happened the other day,
and I also have a few questions
for you, if you don't mind.
Saki...
I guess I shouldn't be
surprised they rejected me.
I really believed
if I apologized
for missing my first interview
they would see it my way
and give me a fair shot.
I mean, it was
out of my control.
Maybe I am naïve
for thinking that.
Seriously though,
I don't think I deserved
to have a bowl of
ramen dumped on me!
I guess they were
just being polite
because of my brother-in-law...
But come on, we're
all adults, you know?
If they really thought they
were so much better than me...
then they should've
just said so!
Thing is...
I already had one job offer...
But when I went
to the interview...
...they kept giving
me this cheesy line
about how they "needed
the youth of today
to pave the way
for tomorrow,"...
but it seemed like what
they really meant was,
"we're looking for
young people willing
to work long hours
for little pay...
so we can take
advantage of them"--
I ended up turning
down their offer.
I think it was a huge mistake.
I don't feel comfortable
going back home...
Don't get me wrong,
I have nothing
but love for my entire family,
especially Ryosuke...
I love him so much!
That's what makes it so hard!
Come over to my place...
I promise to take
care of everything...
Listening to you just
now has helped me realize
what it is I need to do.
So don't stress about
finding a job for now.
You let me worry...
This country's all sortsa
mixed up these days,
and it's not gonna
straighten itself out.
Someone's gonna have to step
in and do something about it.
But just 'cause
I'm gonna play the game,
doesn't mean I wanna punch the
guy who started it any less...
It's 'cause of him,
the Johnnys--
Look--don't worry about the job.
They'll figure out
they were the ones
to mess up by not hiring you.
Just enjoy being
unemployed for now, okay?
Just who... who are you, really?
I don't know...
but, I think I'm
about to find out.
Osugi, would you
please just tell me
what's going on already?
This is the sort of place
you'd take a girlfriend to.
I hope that's not
the way you see me.
Hey, don't go getting
the wrong idea, buddy.
I'm gonna be a working
stooge sooner than later...
So where's the harm in going
to a three-star restaurant
now and then...? HUH?!
Damn it, why the hell'd
you ask me on a date?!
I paid a lotta money
for that meal.
I'm not puking it up!
Why have I been wasting
my time with you, huh?
If you had a boyfriend all
you had to do was tell me...!
Then I never would have gone
after you in the first place!