He became a prince
out of necessity...
He had come to the
realization that the future
we all hoped for would
never come to pass
unless someone volunteered
to become a sacrificial lamb.
It wasn't what he wanted out of
life, but he did it anyway...
He became a prince in this
world without a king...
But what exactly did he have
to do to become a prince...?
The answer still
eludes me today.
Well... Here we are, miss.
And here's your bag.
Oh wow. So this is
the center of the world?
It's much different
than I'd pictured it.
And the fountain's a lot further
away than I'd hoped it'd be.
I wonder if they're mad at me.
Probably...
If I had my phone on, Osugi'd
be calling me right now.
Well I didn't come
down here for nothin'...
Time to put up or shut up.
Darn it! It's too far.
Hey! Young lady!
What did you just throw?
Asshole! You wanna die?!
Hey! Over there! You okay?!
What the...?
Why is that guy naked?
Number Nine is turning out
to be more unique than
I'd ever imagined...
But it ends here.
I see. That's
disappointing to hear.
So you're on his side, huh...?
I'm jealous... Juiz.
Prepare for my return to Japan.
Understood.
I pray for your continuing
service as a savior.
I'm freezing...!
And I'm naked.
A cell phone... and a gun?
The White House.
I know what the
White House is...
and yet I don't have
any idea of who I am.
Hey! Young lady!
What did you just throw?
Asshole! You wanna die?!
Hey! Over there! You okay?!
Actually... I'm the
one in trouble.
Did he get hit?!
Get him!
Well, now's my chance. Ah!
You could've been in
real trouble there.
I'd make a run for it while
you can, if I were you.
Um... I'm not in trouble.
Yeah...? Well I'm pretty
sure it's against the law
to throw stuff
at the White House.
You saw me?
Sorta.
Oh... Well thank you.
Hey, uh... Aren't
you a little cold?
I sure am.
Well then...
Let me... help you out.
You sure...?
I'll probably never
see you again.
It's fine...
Thanks so much for helping me.
Thank you...
I really owe you one.
Bye!
It's empty. Damn it!
I was hoping
there'd be something
that could help me
remember who I am.
Hello. Juiz speaking.
Juiz...? Do I...?
I am your concierge...
I didn't think I would
hear from you again...
but it sounds like you're fine.
Huh...? Tell me...
Would you happen...
to know who I am?
Who you are?
This is the first time
you've erased your memory.
I never received an order to
prepare a new legend for you,
so as to who you are right now,
I can't answer that.
Erased my memory?
The last order
I received was to give you
instructions on where to
go after the procedure...
I'm sending that
address to you now...
That is all.
I hope you succeed and I pray
for your continuing
service as a savior.
This is my home?
If you say so.
That was scary--
No one's gonna believe
me when I tell them...
I guess I... shouldn't be taking
risks in a foreign country.
Oh no! My passport...!
Where did I...
I had it in my coat pocket.
Hey, what's up!
I'm dressed like a fool.
No wonder everyone's
staring at me.
What am I gonna do...?
I have to get it back from him!
Looking for him?
There he is!
Wha... Why'd that guy
just hand over his pants?
This doesn't make any sense!
Hey! Hey! Wait up!
This it?
Crap! Where'd he go?
Wait!
How's it going?
Hey. Dude.
What do you think you're doing?
Uh... My place is on the,
uh, second floor, right?
Try the third floor.
Apartment Three B.
Oh no, I'm running out of time!
If I don't hurry up and get out
of here, I'll miss my flight!
Hey, what's that
guy's room number?
Three B.
Thank you!
Uh, we got a suspicious male
and female couple
on the loose...
I'm sending the pic
from the security camera.
Aw, really?
None of this is ringin' a bell.
Is this really my place?
Perfect fit.
What the hell?
It looks like a
terrorist lives here!
Reminds me of that movie...
What was it called again?
Taxi Driver...!
Except he had a
Mohawk, didn't he...
Some passports...
Man, there's a lot of 'em here.
Maybe I'm more of a Jason
Bourne than Travis Bickle.
They all have my pic...
I'm starting to wonder
if someone's setting me up.
No way...!
I think I really am a terrorist!
Could I have actually
killed people?
Hi.
You're the guy I gave my
coat to earlier, right...?
I hope you don't mind,
but I kind of need it back.
See, I forgot to
take out my passport
and wallet before
I gave it to you...
You can keep the coat.
I don't care about it...
I just need my stuff!
Hey, sure...
Hang on a second, okay?
Saki Morimi...
Born nineteen-eighty-nine.
There we go...! Looks good.
So the name is...
Akira Takizawa...
Cool...! So from now
on I'm Akira Takizawa.
What's he doing in there...?
Hurry up already.
Hello... I need to
ask you something.
Yeah, sure. What?
The girl in this picture...
Is that you?
Um... well... I'm not, uh...
Sorry about that... Ready?
I uh...
Wait a second.
Come this way... please.
Sir, are you Japanese?
I'm gonna need
to see your, Johnny.
Whoa! It sure does look
like me, doesn't it...?
Crazy, huh?
What do you think?
Can you get a
positive ID off this?
Thank you. Have a nice date.
Okay, guess I passed.
Well... Take it easy.
Phew...
Good thing it was
so cold out there...
Let's hurry... this is
getting uncomfortable...
Wha-- What do you mean?
Nothing really...
it's just a little
toasty for my taste...
Hey... When are you
goin' back to Japan?
Right now...
At least I'd hoped to.
Really...?
Then we should
go back together...
Come on...
What...? Wait!
I don't even have my...!
Huh?
I don't have my bag...
I dropped it to
catch up with you.
Wait, you mean way back
by the White House...?
Did you have anything
very important in there?
Just some presents...
and some clothes I like.
Oh... That's too bad...
We can't show our
faces around there.
I'll handle it...
You think you got
enough cash for a cab?
Here, get in. Go on.
Take us to the police...
Fast as you can.
The police, why?
So this passport isn't
a fake, after all...
Lucky me.
Here... One ticket and passport.
Thanks... I take it
you're well-traveled.
Yeah.
I have to admit my heart
was pounding at the embassy...
I didn't think they'd be
able to get us tickets...
Not to mention what would happen
if they found out we were lying.
Technically, we
didn't lie... you know...?
We even filed a police report
that the bags were stolen...
If we hadn't, the embassy
would've never
replaced our tickets.
You have to know how
to play their game
in order to get what you want.
Is that right?
So uh...
You've really gone
out of your way
to help me out today,
and I appreciate that...
but do you mind if
I ask you something
that's been bugging me?
Go ahead.
At the White House...
What exactly were
you doing there...?
Was it some kind
of naked protest?
You want the truth...?
I'm a terrorist.
Kidding... Ha.
It's just a little game we
exchange students like to play.
My buddies were adamant
I carry a gun this time,
even though it was just a fake.
Sounds kind of
extreme for a game.
Yeah, pretty much.
So tell me.
What were you doing in DC?
Huh...? Ah...
It was kind of a
college graduation trip...
We actually went to New York...
but I didn't wanna
come to America
and not see the White House...
so I slipped away.
Oh. Why'd you wanna see
the White House so bad?
I don't know...
Ever since I was a kid...
I've always seen it as
the center of the world.
That must sound strange, huh?
I mean, don't get me wrong,
I don't usually pay much
attention to the U.S.
But one day, I just started
thinking everything
from my little problems...
to the world as a whole,
it all seems to lead back here,
like it's all connected
at the root, ya know?
Besides, there's
some disturbing trends
going on in Japan right now.
It's like this heavy feeling
that we can't do anything
for ourselves anymore.
So I thought since I'm here
I may as well make a
wish for that to change.
That's why you saw
those cops talking to me.
They saw me throw a
quarter over the fence.
Ah... And that's
when I interrupted you.
I actually
reconsidered my wish...
on the way down here...
I guess deep down
I know the U.S.
has nothing to do with
what goes on at home.
I gotcha. Kinda, anyway.
What's that?
But then someone
decided to whip out
a little terrorist act
and everything seemed to...
turn out fine.
Only thing that got
whipped out was my Johnny!
Funny... My name's Saki.
And I... Here ya go.
It says you're Akira Takizawa.
What?
I don't believe this.
You were born January 7th, 1989?
What are the odds
of this happening...?
It's gotta be at
least a million to one!
I gotta say...
Today's been one of the
strangest in my whole life.
Here we are, born
just one day apart...
Maybe destiny has
brought us together...!
Heh... Just kidding.
Or maybe I'm not...
Could he be... the prince I've
been looking for?
Nah, there's no way.
What's up?
You know that heavy feeling
in Japan you were
talking about...?
Looks like this could be it.
There's been a
missile attack on Tokyo.