First you extend your
trip all of a sudden...
And then you stay out all night?
Oh, hey, Ryosuke.
I thought graduation trips
were about leaving
the student in you behind
and taking that first
step into adulthood...
So what happened
with that interview
you had scheduled
the other day...?
I heard that you didn't make it.
Um...
I'm just glad you're
home safe and sound.
I'd head to your room
if I were you...
The last thing you want is
for Asako to chew you out.
This whole
"having no memory" thing
is seriously gettin' annoying...
This business about me
killing twenty-thousand NEET's.
Is it true?
I'm terribly sorry...
I have no information
as to what happened
to them after their abduction.
Okay, that's fair enough...
Let's try a different angle.
Was I the one responsible
for kidnapping them?
You were.
Are you kidding me?!
Then I must've done it.
Okay, next question.
Do you know why I was
chosen to be a Seleção?
I couldn't say.
I was never informed of
the selection criteria.
So... then you
really don't know?
Correct.
Then can you at least tell
me what the Supporter is?
Of course.
The Supporter is one of
the twelve Seleção members,
tasked with the job of
eliminating those
who are deemed unfit
as an effective savior.
And that's me, right?
I'm not at liberty
to divulge that.
So... in other words
I'm just spinning my wheels
trying to ask you about myself.
Yes. Exactly.
Then who am I supposed to ask?
I thought you were
supposed to help me out
in these situations.
Oh right, the Detective
said my best bet
is to ask the other Seleção.
This one sure is busy.
It seems like he's got something
new going on every minute...
Is Number Five
constantly barraging you
with requests all day?
No, not at all...
Whenever I receive
complex requests
I itemize each step,
individually.
I see, so all of these
combine into one request.
I'm seeing here that
someone had an MRI machine
delivered two days ago
from Toyo Medical Tech.
Can you find out
who that is for me?
Order received.
I pray for your continuing
service as a savior.
Just one missile did all that?
Hey! Get away from there!
What an idiot.
Didn't he see the huge sign
and cones back there?
For a second I really thought
he was gonna drive
right off the edge...
You know, like in that movie.
Huh, what movie?
Um, it's that British
flick from the 70's.
I remember a guy
driving his scooter off
a cliff in the last scene.
I just can't think of the title.
You think I would know?
Nobody watches
old movies anymore.
What? Sure they do.
Johnny!
Johnny...! Johnny! Hey!
Hey... get off me!
Stop it...!
Geez, you don't have to bite me!
You buncha useless bastards!!!!
Hey... You okay down there?
It's called Quadrophenia.
Huh?
It's the name of the movie
you two were talking
about just now.
Yeah...! That's it...!
It was right on
the tip of my tongue.
For the record I'm
nothing like that guy...
I may be in a rough spot,
but I'm not that bad off.
How do I get to the
Kanetsu Expressway?
Oh, really...?
I think she just got home
sometime this morning...
Yeah... she told me she stayed
at Micchon's last night.
Saki... Osugi's on
the phone for you...
Are you up or
you still sleeping?
I'm up.
He must be worried.
This is the fifth
time he's called.
Hey, Osugi?
Did I wake you?
Oh, no... Sorry I didn't
call you earlier.
It's alright.
I'm just happy you're okay...
So did you and Micchon
have a fun time last night?
Yeah.
That's cool...
Uh... What ever happened
with your interview?
They understood
once I explained,
so I rescheduled
it for tomorrow.
That's great...!
So, do you want to go together?
I have a prospective employee
training seminar
starting tomorrow.
But... isn't that
out of the way?
Oh no, it's not a big deal...
I know how much of a
beating interviews can be.
If you're with someone
it's easier to build up
your confidence.
Okay... That sounds good.
Awesome... See ya...
I can't believe she lied to me.
What am I doing?
Excuse me. How you doing?
I have a question for you...
I understand someone purchased
an MRI machine recently...
Would you mind telling me
who it was that bought it?
Don't think I've ever
heard that one before...
Uh... if I had to guess,
I'd say it was the Director
who does most of
the purchasing here.
That makes sense...
Look, I really appreciate
you helping me out...
Would you mind calling
up the Director
and telling him
I'm waiting to see him?
I'm sorry, but do you...
have an appointment?
Uh, no...
Tell ya what: Let him know
a Seleção is downstairs...
and I'm sure he'll fit me in.
Here's my number.
There's a lot of
old people here.
I wonder what's up with that?
Paging Doctor Azuma.
Line Five.
Doctor Azuma. Line Five.
You don't wanna
read this trash...
To us patients,
Doctor Hiura is nothing
short of a savior.
I don't care
what the papers say.
Savior?
That's what I said.
I didn't stutter,
you little jackass...
Saki Morimi...
Yeah, hello?
Is this the gentleman
claiming to be a Seleção?
Yes... Um.. My name's Takizawa.
How did you find me?
I was reading the
activity logs on my phone
and saw that an MRI machine
was delivered here, recently.
What is your number, son?
'Scuse me?
Your number.
Which Seleção are you?
Oh, uh, Number Nine.
You don't say...
So Number Nine is the Supporter.
Now hold on just a minute...
Detective Kondo said the
exact same thing to me...
I'm trying to find
out what that means.
Kondo. You mean Number Four?
That's right... Look, Doctor...
I'd prefer it if we
talked face-to-face.
For some reason I decided
to erase my memory,
so I'm kinda in the dark
about a lot of this...
My phone, the fact
that I'm a Seleção,
the game we're all playing.
It's all a blur to me.
All I want...
is for you to answer
a few of my questions.
Come on, I'm asking nicely.
I have no qualms with
you eliminating me...
I'm well aware of the rules...
However I'm reluctant
to be killed
while there's still
money in my account.
I'm... not here for that.
Then I guess the point is moot.
I'm sending you some medicine.
Take the pills to find out
how you came into
possession of the phone.
I guarantee you will
find the information
I have to offer well worth it.
This, uh, medicine
you want me to take.
You mind telling
me what's in it?
It's just a little something.
What the...?
Hey, hold on...
Am I not allowed any
time to think this over?
Ah, forget it.
Damn it...
I think the quack just
poisoned me...! Bastard!
What the hell kinda
doctor is this guy?
Greetings to you.
My name is Mister Outside.
Mister Outside?
Guided by my own highly
personal convictions,
I have taken it upon myself
to select twelve individuals
to act as saviors in an attempt
to rescue this country of ours.
I am calling each of
these saviors Seleção,
and I have appointed one of them
into a very important role,
that of the Supporter.
From this moment forward,
you are no longer just a
citizen, you are a Seleção.
Congratulations.
As for the Supporter,
you can think of that
role as the "twelfth man."
A fierce advocate for the team,
as well as a cold-hearted
sentinel who is always watching.
Be aware that if at any
time your performance
as a Seleção is deemed
to be unsatisfactory,
you should expect to
face swift judgment
at the hands of the Supporter.
So I take it I'm not
the Supporter then?
The answer to that is a
closely guarded secret
known only by me.
It may be you, or it may not.
As for the twelve I have
hand-picked out of millions,
each is an individual who has
an inherently strong desire
to be a Seleção, whether
they realize it or not.
Therefore, participation in
this mission is compulsory.
Refusal is not an option.
The phone I have given you
contains ten billion yen.
How you decide to use the
funds is entirely up to you.
All I ask is that you use
the money to lead this country
towards what you feel
is the right path,
using any methods necessary.
But please note that
the ten billion cannot,
under any circumstances,
be converted to cash.
Should you have any requests,
a concierge is available to
you twenty-four hours a day
by pushing the center
button on your phone.
Upon utilizing your concierge,
the costs of any
requests will be deducted
from the ten billion.
The eleven other
Seleção will be able
to see your purchase in their
phone's activity history.
Be aware that there
are penalties involved
with this venture.
Any Seleção who meets
the following conditions
during the course of
this mission will face
a certain death carried
out by the Supporter.
First: those who wish to abandon
the mission or
attempt to escape...
Second: those who go
long periods of time
without using their phone
and post no results...
Third: those who are
caught using the ten billion
to serve their own,
personal needs rather than
the needs of the
country at large...
And Fourth: those whose
balance reaches zero
before accomplishing
the ultimate goal
of saving the nation.
However, these four rules
are by no means exhaustive.
I would like my chosen twelve
to take full responsibility
for any actions they may take.
And last but not least, the
first Seleção to accomplish
the mission will be deemed the
victor and ultimately survive.
Any remaining Seleção will
be immediately terminated.
There is absolutely
no way around this.
Wait, are you serious...?
So just being picked
is a death sentence!
That is all I have
for you at this time...
Remember, I chose
you for a reason.
If you can tap into the hidden
power I know you possess,
and become the first Seleção
to successfully save this nation
from the peril it faces,
you will be brought
to my location at once.
Noblesse oblige...
I sincerely pray that you
will become our savior...
Don't let me down.
I'm curious, Doc.
Did you get the same
dog and pony show
when you got your phone?
I suppose it was a
little over-the-top.
Why'd it have to be like this?
I wanted to see my
final request granted today
in front of the Prefectural
Assembly meeting...
I wasn't certain if you
were the Supporter or not...
That's why I drugged you.
What you just
experienced is identical
to my own initiation.
For me it was after
stumbling into a taxi drunk
and covered in vomit.
Only then did I notice the
strange box staring at me.
Well you didn't have
to replicate the vomit.
So was it any different for you?
Did you choose to join the game
or were you forced to, like me?
I had no choice...
but... in a way
I didn't mind it...
You see, I'm a brain surgeon,
but it limits me to helping
only one person at a time.
And I know I'm capable
of doing more.
After all, the number
of lives a doctor can save
in his career pales
in comparison
to the population as a whole.
Take a look at something.
I had a law changed that
allowed me to transform
this neighborhood into
a self-sustaining utopia
where patients and their
families can live and work.
Uh...
My story is a simple one...
Japan was on the verge
of abandoning its elderly...
so I decided to
exhaust my ten billion
creating a private hospital...
where we could give them
work and low-cost health care.
The only thing left to
do is ensure the system
is self-manageable,
preferably by the government.
Then my work will be done.
I just scanned your history...
They all look like bribes to me.
Juiz is absolutely brilliant...
She was able to win
over the entire Assembly
in what would take any
normal person decades.
Juiz did that...? Wait.
Does this mean that...
me and the other
Seleção are going to be
terminated by the Supporter?
No. That won't happen.
Honestly, I created this
hospital and community
for personal reasons
and nothing more.
In the end I doubt
it will impress
Mister Outside in the slightest.
If all this work
isn't enough to win,
then what the hell does he
expect the rest of us to do...?
This Mister Outside
sounds like the devil.
Funny you should say that.
I see him as more
of a generous god.
You know...
we've been pulled into a
game of life and death here.
I don't want to
die anytime soon...
but how about if I give
you half my money...
to keep you going?
You're a thoughtful kid
and I appreciate that...
but I've never had any intention
on actually winning this game.
Don't hesitate to fire away
with any questions
you may still have...
Although if you ask me
who it is you are...
I'm not sure I could
answer that one.
Okay. What've I done up to now?
I've spent around
two billion so far.
Well, you bought
the shopping mall
in that ghost town...
five hundred
shipping containers...
and some Foreign Office
entertainment...
It would seem to
me that you've been
quite the busy guy lately.
Yeah, but have I...
killed a lot of people?
Sorry, but that's one question
I'm not able to answer.
You sure about that?
You had a goal that
was so important to you
it was worth wiping
away your memory...
Judging solely by
your activity logs,
the old Number Nine
was an appealing,
fearless and
highly-driven individual.
You had a good life you
were willing to give up...
in order to bet everything
on your future self...
That's why I believe you should
continue on the
path you're on now.
I'm glad I got to
meet you before I die.
Come on, don't
talk like that...!
You're still...
I hope you turn out
to be the true savior.
Juiz speaking.
Hello again...
I just wanted to thank you
for all your help...
If it weren't for you,
I never would have been
able to accomplish all I did.
That's nonsense...
I should be apologizing
for not doing enough.
No... you were great...
Thanks, Juiz.
So... You're the Supporter, huh?
All right.
I'm ready to die...
I have no regrets.
The Supporter's here?!
Doctor Hiura...
You deserve better than this.
I hate this game...
What kind of a maniac would
think this is a good idea?
I wanna deck the bastard...
who gave me this phone.