It's turning into a slum.
Yeah...
but it looks like people are
still in the apartments.
You live in an
apartment too, right?
Who knows...
Judging by the address,
I'd say it's a house.
Yeah, right.
It should be that way.
The missile hit over there,
so I bet your
place is still standing.
Mhmm. The thing is,
all those buildings are dark,
like they're condemned.
We should at least check it out.
Here we are.
Are you sure this
is it...? I'm not.
It's the right address.
It worked.
There should be a light
switch around here somewhere.
Wow... Not the kind of place...
I was expecting.
Tell me about it.
Is anything here ringing a bell?
You found the key to get
in like you'd done it before.
I feel something
but I can't place it.
Takizawa!
What the...
I got spooked... Aw, cute!
What are you
doing here, little guy?
Hey, there!
I think we can say for sure
this is where you live...
I mean, look at him.
That little puppy obviously
knows who you are.
You're right...
You sure are friendly,
aren't ya, little buddy?
I know this is outta
your jurisdiction...
Thanks for sticking
your neck out.
I'm just doing my job.
Oh and hey, would you
mind sticking around
here for an hour or so...?
If I'm not back by then,
head home to your
wife and kids, okay?
Thanks, pal.
You've gotta be kidding me.
The kid actually lives here?
Sure enough, it says
right here in the log,
he bought the entire place.
You're not the only one
who wants to wipe your memory...
I just hope you're inside.
He wants us to go upstairs.
I can't believe
you live in a mall!
How cool is that?
It makes me wonder
what kind of a
person I really am.
It's kinda creepy,
straight out of Dawn
of the Dead, ya know?
Is that a movie?
Mm-hm.
I'm sure if we
start looking around
we'll find something
that'll help you.
The paper was still
being delivered,
and I'm sure there's
some mail, too.
We may even find the paperwork
for when you bought the place.
No way...! This is where
that photo was taken.
So this is definitely the
home of Akira Takizawa...
but what exactly
was I doing here?
Takizawa...! Are you okay?!
Did you find anything?
Nope, nothing yet.
This must be the movie theater.
You trying to get us into
the late show, little guy?
Is this where you live?
Oh, wow...! What in the...
This apartment is amazing!
Oh yeah...
You definitely live here.
I'm not so sure.
But just look
around you...! Like...
You know more
details about the movies
you've seen than you
do about yourself.
How much do you wanna
bet you worked here
at some point as
the theater manager?
Manager, huh?
Oh look.
You can see
ground zero from here.
Sure can.
Oh! Hey!
Are there any movies that you're
really itching to see...?
It can be any movie at all.
I can play it on the big screen.
I'm not sure.
Remember, I don't
watch many movies.
You can't think of
one movie you like...?
For instance, what did you
see on your first date?
Uh, well let's see...
There's a French movie
with a dolphin and
a diver I really liked.
Ah, nice one.
And yet you still don't recall
any details about yourself.
I know, huh?
So what is it about that
one that made you pick it?
Someone who I've always liked...
really loves that movie...
Hey Juiz, I was hoping you
could do me a favor...
There's a specific
movie I'm looking for...
Yeah... I'm in the
theater right now.
Police?
Understood.
I'm scanning the database
for the films that are
currently on file there.
Please standby.
Noblesse oblige.
I pray for your continuing
service as a savior.
Yeah, well... I can at
least try to be a gentleman.
Look at this place...
It's a dump.
I've seen refugee camps
in better shape than this.
Oh man, look at all
these cell phones.
Okay... I get it now...
This kid was involved
in the disappearance
of all those NEET losers.
So a Seleção was...
behind the attacks
and the disappearances.
If I'd paid attention
to his history
rather than blowing
all that cash...
I'd be up for a promotion
right about now.
But... I'm getting myself
a new lease on life
and a cool eight billion
to go along with it...
Simply not my problem anymore.
Oh right...
I can't have my cell phone going
off while the movie's playing.
The number you are
trying to reach is
either out of range
or no longer in service.
Please try again later.
Thank you.
I have to hand it to Osugi.
You can't fault him
for lack of trying.
I think he's fighting
a losing battle.
Tell everyone I'm staying
at your place tonight.
Pretty please...
I just told Asako that,
so don't get me in trouble.
Hey, when did you get this?
It was around eleven or so.
Uh... What's going on?
We're going home... So tired.
I wonder where she's
really staying.
Maybe Saki's right.
I really could've been
the projectionist here,
just like in Cinema Paradiso.
Wow! The screen's gigantic!
Here goes.
Where is he?
There you are.
You always come to the movies
by yourself, Detective...?
Since you're alone,
I assume you're not here
to arrest me, huh...
You been watching me?
Yeah... See?
So I take it you came
here to talk shop...?
Actually... I was
hoping you'd stop by,
since we got cut
short last time.
That's nice...
So kid, have you been
checking out my logs recently?
By logs...
You mean the ones
on here, right...?
By the way,
what is a Seleção...?
Look, the thing is,
I'm suffering from amnesia.
I literally don't remember
one detail about myself...
Now if you don't mind,
I'd appreciate the chance to
pick your brain for a while.
So then...
you really did wipe
your memory, huh...
Where's Takizawa...?
Huh, pup?
Interesting...
So Harima Neuroscience
Institute's brainwashing
program really did
the trick, didn't it...
I may have to try it
for myself sometime...
But first... I'm gonna
need you to hand over
that phone you got in your hand.
You got way too
careless, big guy.
What the hell is
that phone, anyway...?
How much money did
yours start with?
Huh... Stubborn prick.
I'm taking whatever
cash you have on here...
If I had to guess,
I'd say you started with
ten billion like I did.
The joke's on us, though.
'S no way you can change the
world with a measly ten bil'.
It's impossible...
The bastards who forced us
into this game should die!
Mister...
You've got one helluva kick...
The girl...
She has... nothing...
to do with... this, 'kay?
Killing her would
cost me money...
It'd be a waste of my time.
Oh, right...
I may as well give you
a little heads up...
When it comes to
Noblesse phones...
as soon as the
balance hits zero,
someone named the Supporter
will track you down
and give you two to the head...
Those are the
rules we live by...
That's tough luck
for you, kiddo...
The girl may be safe,
but you're a dead man.
The score's even now...
Detective.
I wonder who
this Supporter is...
Another mystery.
I'm sorry.
It doesn't look like I'll...
be able to make the late show.
Hey, there.
You wouldn't happen to know
where Takizawa went,
would you...?
If he didn't wanna
spend time with me,
he could have just said so.
Ha, nice message.
Well... Time we paid
the Detective a visit.
I now have enough money for us
to play around with for
the rest of our lives...
I called you a taxi...
See you in...
Kabu... kicho... Bye
There, just spent my last yen.
The phone's identical.
You'd think it'd work
the same way...
Damn it... Shit...
I'll have to call Juiz.
Hello. Juiz speaking.
Hey there...
I got a question
I wanna run by you.
What would happen if someone
were to get ahold
of my phone...?
Can just anyone use it?
It uses fingerprint
recognition technology,
so it would effectively
be rendered useless...
Why, is there a problem?
Oh no... Just making sure.
Thanks... Gotta go...
Son of a... bitch!
Dammit!
How do I always...
fuck things up?!
Thanks, Saki.
Let's go already... Answer.
I know you can hear me...
Come on, Detective Kondo...
I'm just trying to
make a nice gesture
by returning your
precious ID badge...
The least you can
do is say hello.
Dammit... How did you...
It's about time... So tell me.
Where are you right now?
I'm in the middle
of Kabukicho...
You better get
your ass over here!
Kabukicho...
Um, how do I get there again?
Come on... Stop dicking around!
How quickly you forget.
Remember? I wiped my memory.
Go towards Kiba and
hit the expressway.
Misae.
Hey, what are you
doing here... honey?
"Enough money
for us to play with
for the rest of our lives"?
Hold on... How did you...?
When you text your mistress...
try not to send it to your wife.
It's over... my darling.
You okay, Detective?
Shut up, kid... Shut up.
Let me call you an ambulance.
You need help.
Don't bother
wasting your time...
It looks like... I'm done for.
You can't just give up...
I still need to--
Listen. There are
ten others besides us...
All are Seleção and they all
have the same exact phone.
Seleção are people...
just like you and me,
forced into playing
this idiotic game...
whether they want to or not.
You can see their activity
logs on your phone.
Your best bet at finding them
is by tracing their steps
through those logs...
Once you do,
ask them who you are...
Of course, this is assuming
any of 'em are willing
to meet with a dangerous
Seleção like yourself,
so don't be
surprised if they run.
Wait... I'm dangerous?
Damn straight...
You rounded up
twenty-thousand NEET's
and tried to kill them...
and that is the truth.
No wait... Of course...
You're the Supporter,
aren't you?
It all makes sense now...
That's why Misae...
Look Detective, I don't know
what you're talking about.
Well, you got me...
Take this and split, kid.
Said get outta here!
I lost this one.
In the beginning, I...
I tried to do the right thing...
God knows I... tried...