Is ASEAN movin' stocks and
adjusting interest rates
fast enough?
No. It appears the Southeast
Asian Financial District
is teetering on
the brink of collapse.
Well, that's no good.
Let's prepare for C.
If a Financial District
goes bust
does that mean
its country'll disappear?
That's right. You weren't around
for the Lehman Shock, were you?
You've no clue how
serious this is. Sorry.
You're better off not knowing
the answer to that question.
Aw c'mon, just give it
to me straight!
Well, the short answer is yes.
It will vanish.
Whoa, that's crazy! Wait. You're
sayin' it could happen now?!
Before the Lehman Shock,
there was a country in
the Caribbean Sea. It was one of
the great economic world powers
called the Caribbean Republic.
But when the South American
Financial District fell
it was wiped off the map.
Who would've thought
a bustling city like Tokyo
could turn into
this ghost town?
You know, if things don't
start pickin' up around here
I'm gonna be outta
business in no time.
Lemme guess, that's
your way of tellin' me
the country's on its last leg?
Smart lady!
Hate to say it, but
I don't think I'm gonna be
doing business in yen anymore.
It's practically worthless.
All our future transactions
will have to be paid
in American dollars,
or better yet,
make it Chinese yuan.
So your homeland is completely
falling apart around you
and the only thing
you're worried about
is switching currency?
Well, to be fair,
it's not like I got to choose
where I was born.
Have any new info for me?
There's a member of the Starling
Guild who might switch sides
if he's given
a talking to, that is.
Convince him to switch
and I'll pay you three times
the usual in dollars,
yuan, whatever you want.
Oh. Miss Sato? I also got
an interesting tidbit of info
on Kimimaro Yoga.
Then let's hear it.
You're familiar
with his asset, right?
From the first moment
I laid eyes on her,
I've had this weird feeling
I've seen her somewhere before.
Big deal.
The reason she looks familiar
is because she used to work
alongside the boy's father.
Couldn't care less. If you wanna
make money off info like that,
you should be talking
to the kid, not me.
Well, I'll be damned.
It appears I've misread you.
Hey Hanabi.
Hey Kimimaro. Need somethin'?
No, I guess not. How'd student
teaching go? Did you like it?
I did. It was a lotta work,
you know?
But I had a good time, too.
Awesome.
That all?
Oh. Yeah. I'm sorry.
I don't mean to bug you.
Well, you are.
Kakuta?
Sorry, man.
The one thing that's
hit me the hardest
since I started my
investigation of the District
is the endless amount of
statistical data I've read
indicating that the decline of
the human race is imminent.
It looks bad
but this was expected.
We're in the next stage. Early.
There's no reason to worry.
Oh, I'm so sorry.
Let me get that.
What's he doing up there?
Professor Ebara!
Yoga. How've you been?
Is there something wrong?
You look pale.
Well, yeah. I'm worried about
you. Why're you up here?
Because, this is my last
ditch effort to get my kids
back somehow. I'm afraid
jumping is the only way.
I've tried everything else.
I got rid of my possessions
hoping it might result
in some kind of trade;
I even scrapped
my years of research.
My life is all that I have left
to give up.
Professor, I know you're upset
but you have to realize
jumping won't bring them back.
I know I'm taking a risk
and I could end up dead
but that's a chance I'm willing
to take. If the bank sees
how desperate I am,
maybe they'll return
my wife and kids to me.
I'll have my family back.
Look, just because
you offer them your life
doesn't mean the bank'll
trade it for theirs.
I know. Truthfully,
I just can't take it anymore.
When I came back from our
deal, I went out drinking
instead of going straight home.
I was terrified- I had no idea
what fate might
be waiting for me.
When I finally walked
in the door and realized
my children were gone.
Well, I was heartbroken.
At the same time,
I felt relieved because
I thought it would
be so much worse.
But ever since they were
taken away from me
I don't have any drive.
It's as though I've
lost the will to live.
I've tried to distract
myself with my research
but it just doesn't work. I
can't concentrate worth a damn.
How could I have been such
a fool? When Masakaki asked
for my future as collateral,
I handed it right over to him
with no questions asked.
I never would've done that
if I had known going bankrupt
meant losing it.
There's gotta be something
we can do to get it back.
There must be. I'll go ask
around the Financial District.
So don't jump!
Look at you, playing the hero.
I didn't want to get
wrapped up in all this.
I just wanna be
an ordinary guy again.
No, it's good. You've finally
started to move forward!
I'm proud of you, Yoga.
It's about time you started
asserting yourself.
I don't understand,
why'd you come here?
There's something I gotta do.
And it's gonna cost me
a lot of Midas money.
Unfortunately, that means
the next time we deal
I'll probably be a little
low on funds. I know that's
going to make things
harder on you.
I can handle it.
You're not angry?
I'm sure you've got a
perfectly good reason for it.
Spend away. It's fine with me.
You just do what you gotta do.
Masa-kaki!
Ma-sa-ka-ki!
There's no need to yell.
I'm standing right here.
It's not nearly as difficult
to get your attention
as I thought it'd be.
All I had to do was scream.
Might I suggest you try
a whisper next time?
My ears are quite sensitive.
Sure.
Thanks. Now how may I be
of assistance, Mr. Yoga?
Do you remember Daisuke Ebara? I
was forced to deal against him
and he ended up going bankrupt?
Yes!
I want you to give him back
the future you were holding
as collateral. I'm willing
to pay you for it.
I'll give you 100 times
the amount he had
before we started the deal.
What?! Has he gone crazy?!
That's funny. I had no idea
that you were such a comedian.
How much is it gonna be?
I would love to take
you up on your offer
but I'm afraid
that's just not possible.
Why not?! If I pay the bank 100
times his original fortune,
that's a huge profit!
I don't make the rules,
I simply enforce them.
Those decisions are made
by the man upstairs.
Fine, then take me
up there to see him!
I can't do that. The boss man
isn't much of a people person.
Boss man? Wait! Hey!
Enjoy the rest of your day!
You wanna get a bankrupt
Entre's future back, huh?
That's gonna be tough.
I figured you'd be
the guy to talk to.
You got it, kid! Now,
lemme warn ya, there've been
several Entrees who've tried
to do the same thing as you.
And as far I know, not a single
one of them was successful.
Daisuke Ebara. When he went
bankrupt against you,
his two rug-rats disappeared.
Well, three if you count
the bun in the oven.
You know, if you're feelin'
guilty and you wanna
make amends, there's a much
easier way to go about it.
What's that?!
You compensate the guy!
You know, like when somebody's
killed in a car accident
and the victim's family
is paid big money
for their loss.
I'd say three kids
is gonna cost ya at least
a few hundred million.
Paying him off isn't gonna
make you feel any better!
He wants his children back.
Not money.
That's true.
As Singapore's currency
and interest rates rise,
its company's share
prices are plummeting.
It's worrisome, especially
since their government
hasn't proposed
a single relief measure.
This recession has hit every
industrialized nation--
The Southeast Asian
Financial District's
at the end of its rope.
That's not good. It's hitting
a little too close to home.
C.
Where's Isurugi?!
He should be here by now.
Chill out,
he's probably on his way.
I'm sorry I'm running late.
Something came up
as I was leaving work.
Why didn't you call and
give us a head's up, man?!
Timing's everything. If
we're off by even a minute
it can break us.
Reading from
Mr. Mikuni's script?
Why, you little!
You can't fault the man
for attending to business.
Now that he's here,
he'll just have to
work harder to catch up.
Thank you for understanding.
So how is our
current situation looking?
The Southeast Asian Financial
District is crashing harder
and faster than I anticipated.
I think it's time we shift
our priorities and focus
on defensive fund-raising.
I want every member
of the Starling Guild
to challenge
a nonmember to a deal.
And steal his fortune.
You're not worried that might
affect the real world?
If this situation progresses,
it'll threaten
our very existence.
We can't afford to waste time
worrying how our actions
might upset the balance.
We gotta pick our opponents.
Whoa! These are the top
three Entres who aren't
in the guild, huh?
I'll take on the
strongest dude-
he looks like
a good match for me.
What about you?
Doesn't matter.
Guess I'll take number two.
You'd better not mouth off
to that guy, Shindo,
'Cause if you piss
him off, it's adieu to you.
You think you can
do better, ya freak?!
Excuse me. Where can I find
Professor Daisuke Ebara?
Probably at the funeral?
But it's not here-
it's in Hokkaido.
Evidently that's his hometown.
Someone died?
Yeah, he did.
Professor Ebara's dead?!
He was hit by a car.
Sorry, I thought you knew.
Dear Miss Hanabi.
I hope you're good.
You were the best student
teacher in the whole world.
Class isn't the same
without you.
We decided to write you
letters 'cause we miss you.
You're a really nice lady
and we had a lot of fun
the week you were here.
I wish you could've stayed
our teacher forever.
You should come back and visit
us soon. It would be fun!
I hope I was your favorite
student! Love, Yuna Kimura.
It was terrible. Professor Ebara
was hit by a drunk driver.
What makes it worse is the
driver said he was racing
to make the green light.
And he didn't see the
professor standing there.
You'd think
a person's life would be
more important
than making good time.
Now don't lose it, okay?
I won't!
Hey, that's my money!
Give it back!
Here ya go.
Thank you!
Our world has been changing
right before our very eyes.
The shifts are so subtle most
people never even notice,
but it's steadily getting
worse and worse.
This can't be happening.
What the hell is going on?!
Well, well,
if it isn't Mr. Yoga!
This is the first time we've met
in this world, isn't it?
Maybe it's some kinda sign from
the universe. Want a crepe?
On me. I got a whole truck
full of 'em.
So tell me. Why do you run a
crepe truck? You've gotta make
a ton of money with all your
information trafficking.
You don't need
any more, do you?
Of course I do! You can never
have enough money.
"The more you have
the greedier you get."
Yeah, I would imagine
that's true with most people.
I'm different 'cause
I want more than money,
I want consumer confidence.
If they think they can trust ya,
people are more likely
to throw big bucks your way.
Lemme give you an example.
Why do you buy
information from me?
Because I need it.
But why me? How do you know
what I'm telling you is true?
'Cause Mr. Mikuni introduced you
and I trust him.
My point exactly.
Your trust in him brought me
a new paying client.
Building consumer confidence
in my business allows me
to earn more.
My profits continue to rise
as long as people have faith
in the value of their money.
If they lose faith it's
worthless. The same applies
to futures being
held as collateral.
Guess you could say that.
You have to ask yourself.
Whether you have more
faith in the future
or in the power of money.
I can't believe we haven't
decided on a name for you yet.
Why don't we ask
your Daddy what he thinks?
Do you have any ideas, honey?
What's the perfect name
for our little girl?
Mashu.
You look tuckered out, kiddo.
What the hell are you doing?!
Is he for real?!
What a waste!
If you don't need the cash,
then give it to me!
You're not gonna yell at me?
I thought you'd be mad
about me wasting
my money like this.
If this is what you wanna do
then I'm not gonna stop you.
Go right ahead.
I'm proud of you
for being so bold.
I don't want this stuff anymore.
I'm not willing to steal
anyone else's future for it.
In the end, it's just paper.
Look how it burns.
Has this experience
taught you anything?
Now I know that having
a future is more important
than having money because I
have more faith in the future.
You do realize burning your
Midas money isn't gonna
do any damage to the
Financial District, right?
Consumer confidence is what
gives it its value. Not you.
You're not gonna make it
worthless by burning it.
Sure, you may
destroy a few bills
but the bank will just
end up printing more.
Yeah, that's true.
If you wanna do something,
you're gonna have to act fast.
The country's heading
into the final stage.
Once we hit it
there's no turning back.
Is something wrong?
I'm beginning to wonder if maybe
what he said to me was right.
What who said?
Ko Sennoza.
If all we have left is
a future of
missed opportunities
then the present
has no meaning.
Didn't we cover this?
He had it wrong.
How can you be sure?
Even though it may be slightly
altered by our actions,
the future itself
will always be there.
But if it's miserable,
who wants it?
I do.
No, according to what
you told me, you don't.
You said people are too stressed
to worry about tomorrow.
Does that mean we should
sacrifice the people
in our future to hold onto
the people who're alive now?
You were wrong about Sennoza!
He wasn't just someone who
could afford to look
towards the future.
He wanted to do what's best
for all of mankind!
If the present were to disappear
so would the future.
It exists for the sake
of the future!
You have news?
When the Southeast Asian
District falls looks like
Singapore's gonna
go down with it.
So, it's begun.
How are we on funds?
We're low.
It's barely enough.
We can't worry about that right
now we'll just have to make do.
It's time to make our move.
We'll fight off C the best that
we can. We'd better head back.
Right.
C? I dunno what you're up to
but it can't be good.
Keep your mouth shut,
and don't dare get in my way.
Maybe you'll learn something.