[screaming]
Where are we?
--[MAN'S VOICE] He intends only
his own gain and he is...
[ITANEDA] Here ya go, boss.
Splendid, yes?
The Bank of Midas Plaza.
It's the heart
of the Financial District!
[MAN'S VOICE] ...to promote
an end which was no part of
his intention.
Nor is it always the worse
for the society
that it was not part of it...
[KIMIMARO]
Whoa, what is that?
[MASAKAKI] An Asset.
A personal Asset to be precise.
They assist Entres
during a deal.
[KIMIMARO]
A what?
[MASAKAKI]
Take a look above you.
That ticker will tell you
everything you need to know
about your dealing opponents.
[KIMIMARO] Opponents?
[MASAKAKI] Each week Entres
are required to participate
in a competition
known as a "deal."
Consider it your
"price of admission."
At any rate, let's carry on.
[SOICHIRO] A rookie, huh?
He's not gonna
last long around here.
[Q] What makes you say that?
[SOICHIRO] That kid
wouldn't hurt a fly.
How can you be so sure?
You wanna wager on it?
♪ opening song ♪
Your opponent's
waiting for you.
[KIMIMARO] I'm so screwed.
The first thing
you'll want to do
is run your fingers
over the face of your card.
[KIMIMARO gasps]
What's it say?
What? Oh!
Uh.
[KIMIMARO]
It looks like M-Mashu?
That's my name? Well,
I guess it could be worse.
At any rate, I look forward
to dealing with you.
So, wait,
is this girl my Asset?
That's correct.
[KIMIMARO] Seems kinda
underwhelming
compared to what
that other guy's got.
[MASAKAKI] Assets are the
embodiment of their Entre's
future. Nothing more,
nothing less. Uh-oh! Looks like
the deal is about to start.
Good luck!
[KIMIMARO] Come back!
How am I gonna beat this guy
with such a puny Asset?
What'd you do that for?
You think you can insult me
and get away with it, moron?
[MASHU] C'mon, let's do this!
[SAKAMAKI'S CARD]
Open deal.
[KIMIMARO'S CARD]
[SAKAMAKI'S CARD]
Micro.
--[KIMIMARO] Aw man, that hurt.
--[SAKAMAKI'S CARD] Direct.
[KIMIMARO] Thanks Mashu!
[SAKAMAKI] Gyiyg!
Would you please just tell me
what the hell's going on?
[MASHU] Come on! If you don't
at least try to protect yourself
you're gonna go bankrupt!
[KIMIMARO] Bankrupt?
What's that circle?
[MASHU] It shows
how much money you have.
[KIMIMARO screaming]
[MASHU] Pick up the pace!
Are you trying
to get your face blown off?
I didn't think a newbie
like you would dodge
two attacks in a row.
Let's go, Gyiyg!
[SAKAMAKI]
Micro: 300,000!
[SAKAMAKI'S CARD]
Micro!
[KIMIMARO screaming]
[KIMIMARO AND WASHU
crying out]
[KIMIMARO] You okay?
You aren't hurt, are you?
Of course I'm hurt,
you idiot!
You have no idea
how serious a deal is do you?
Well, it looks like the rookie's
giving him a run for his money.
[KIMIMARO] If we keep this up
we're gonna be killed!
Let's forfeit.
It doesn't matter if I lose.
Don't you get it? If you
go bankrupt it's all over!
Another Micro should do it.
[SAKAMAKI]
Micro: 900,000!
[SAKAMAKI'S CARD]
Micro!
[KIMIMARO] If I just tell
the guy I wanna quit
I'm sure he'll understand!
[MASHU] Yeah, right!
Don't waste your breath!
Mashu, no!
Are you okay? Hey, answer me!
[MASHU]
You've gotta run!
Look you can't
keep worrying about me,
I can take care of myself!
[KIMIMARO]
But.
[MASHU]
You've gotta hurry!
Damn you!
You can't keep this up
or you'll go broke.
Oh yeah? Why you
little smartass!
[SAKAMAKI]
Gyiyg! Micro: 3 million!
[SAKAMAKI'S CARD]
Micro!
[TAKEDAZAKI] Talk about
a one-sided deal, huh?
[SOICHIRO]
Hardly worth watching.
Even for you, Takedazaki.
On the contrary,
as an information dealer,
I can't miss it.
Why?
There's still a small chance
this kid could
turn this thing around and
end up winning his first deal.
Which would make him the
second amateur Entre to do so.
You're such a nosy bastard.
Don't I know it. But I
thought you of all people
might appreciate
my curiosity, Mr. Mikuni.
[KIMIMARO]
Does it hurt?
[MASHU]
Big time. But I'll be fine.
[KIMIMARO]
Are you sure?
[MASHU]
Yeah. Just give me a minute.
I'm sorry. This is
all my fault, isn't it?
[MASHU chuckling]
[MASHU] It's weird for an Entre
to worry about his Asset.
But why wouldn't I be worried?
How am I supposed to feel
when someone gets hurt?
Jeez. I don't even know
what I'm doing here yet.
[MASHU] The rules are simple.
If you get hit by an opponent's
attack you lose money.
But if you buy an attack
and hit them you make a profit.
Do you still wanna forfeit?
It's going to take me
a while to get this,
but I want you to teach me
how to fight. Will you?
[MASHU]
Okay.
[MASHU gasping]
[MASHU crying]
[KIMIMARO]
Mashu!
[MASHU] Don't worry.
I'm a fast healer.
[SAKAMAKI]
Too late for that!
All right, Gyiyg,
finish them off!
Micro: 5 million!
[SAKAMAKI'S CARD]
Micro!
Swipe your hand across the card
and make an investment!
Like this?
[MASHU] Mezzoflation:
10 million! Do it!
[KIMIMARO'S CARD]
Mezzoflation.
Okay, Mezzoflation.
10 million!
[KIMIMARO'S CARD]
Scorched Earth.
Scorched Earth!
[impressed chatter]
[TAKEDAZAKI] I can't believe
he used Mezzoflation
in his first deal!
[KIMIMARO]
Whoa! Nice job!
No kidding, that was so cool!
How could I lose to a newb?
[KIMIMARO'S CARD]
Closing.
You have gain.
[MASAKAKI] Congratulations!
Good work out there!
Where's Mashu?
[MASAKAKI] The deal's over.
You won! Be proud of yourself!
[KIMIMARO]
I don't care about that!
I-I wanna know what
happened to Mashu!
[MASAKAKI] Are you talking
about your Asset?
[KIMIMARO]
Of course I am! Who else?
[MASAKAKI]
She's safe.
Well, that's a relief.
She's okay.
[MASAKAKI] Don't worry, you'll
see her again soon enough.
In fact, we should schedule
your next deal--
[KIMIMARO fainting]
[MASAKAKI]
You don't look so good.
Hello? Mr. Yoga,
can you hear me?
Oh dear, you've completely worn
yourself out, haven't you?
Very well, I'll see you home
safely but just this once.
[CROWD murmuring]
New kid put on quite a show.
[TAKEDAZAKI] Good for him!
You must be happy!
And why is that?
Call it a hunch, but you were
rooting for the new kid,
weren't you?
You know, for an
information dealer,
you aren't very well informed.
[TAKEDAZAKI] Like I said, just
a hunch. If anyone was going to
root for the rookie
I'd think it'd be you.
[SOICHIRO] You won the bet,
Q. Here you go.
However unlikely
it seemed, somehow,
I still had a feeling
that boy would not lose.
An odd sentiment, I know,
especially considering
he is the only Entre
to win his first deal
without knowing the rules,
since you came here.
[Q] Not only that, he was
eager to help his Asset
just as you had helped me.
[SOICHIRO]
What are you trying to say, Q?
You think he's gonna
turn out like me?
It is too early
to speculate at this point.
Mikuni.
That's odd-- it's not like him
to go out of his way to watch
someone else's deal. Right?
[ITANEDA
laughing creepy laughter]
C.
[yelling]
[sighing]
Did you think
it was all a dream?
[KIMIMARO screaming]
I have to admit, you did
quite well for your first time!
You must be simply beaming
with satisfaction!
You think I'd be happy about
something like that? No way!
Whenever you're in
the Financial District,
time stands still in this world
so your deals won't affect
your daily routine.
I'll be back
to pick you up next week.
You mean I have to
do this every week?
Don't blame me. I'm not
the one who made the rules.
Then who did?
Anyway, I'll see you next time!
But what do I do until then?
Your life isn't
any different than before.
But now you have cash to spend.
And although we don't choose
to enforce a code of silence,
you might want
to keep quiet all the same
since I doubt anyone
would believe you. Adieu.
Oh yes! One last thing,
you can chat with your Asset
through your Midas Card.
Go ahead and try it!
Through my card, huh?
Hello in there?
How does this work anyway?
[MASHU]
Need something?
You sound like
you're feeling better.
Yeah, just getting back
my strength.
You really are an odd one.
[KIMIMARO]
You think so?
Quit worrying, I'm an Asset.
[KIMIMARO] You were hurt!
It's only normal to worry!
Normal, huh?
Sure, whatever you say.
[KIMIMARO] Do you have
a problem with me acting like
a normal human being?
[MASHU] Is that all?
'Cause I'm kinda busy.
[KIMIMARO]
For now, I guess.
[MASHU] Well, if you need me,
you know where to find me.
I wonder if
I'll ever get used to this.
It can be a bit awkward
for everyone, at first.
I thought you left already?
No, I'm still here.
There has got to be some way
for me to get out of this mess.
[MASAKAKI] If you went bankrupt,
you'd be banished
from the Financial District.
However, I wouldn't recommend
that as it can cause severe
repercussions in this world.
I suggest that you keep dealing.
And not just for the money.
It may help you view the world
in a whole new light.
[MASAKAKI chuckling]
Give it some time.
What's that supposed to mean?
[general chatter]
[ATM 1B] Please don't forget
to take your withdrawal.
Thank you for your business.
Have a nice day.
Ones, tens,
hundreds, thousands.
Thirty three million,
five hundred thousand?
[TEACHER 2A] What we're talking
about is risk assessment.
An objective evaluation
of risk in which assumptions
and uncertainties are clearly
considered and presented.
Wow, it looks like
somebody was hungry.
[KIMIMARO]
Yeah, kinda.
I couldn't help but notice
you seemed to have
a tough time
paying attention in class.
[KIMIMARO] I'm just tired.
I couldn't concentrate.
I saw you playing
with that cash card thing.
[KIMIMARO]
Hey can I ask you something?
If you had ten million yen,
how would you spend it?
I would save it.
That's what
I figured you'd say.
In this day and age, nobody
knows what's gonna happen next.
You gotta save in case
an emergency pops up.
[NEWSCASTER] In other news, a
Saitama woman has been charged
with murder after suffocating
her two year old toddler.
Investigators say that the woman
recently lost her job...
[HANABI] Not again. Honestly,
what is wrong with this world?
[IOGI] It's a gift from Chairman
Dallas of the Peyton Company.
[SOICHIRO] A '29, huh?
He's really feeling generous.
[IOGI chuckles] I think it's an
attempt to win you over. He's
been plotting the downfall of
Fox-McRainer for some time now.
[SOICHIRO] One bottle of wine
and he thinks he can
use me to take down
a rival company?
[IOGI] By the way, local
opposition seems to have turned
the current administration
against us
on the public utilities matter.
[MAN 2A] As usual,
the masses are short-sighted.
[SOICHIRO] If the public won't
work with us, we'll go private.
We'll just have
to grease a few palms.
[IOGI] Consumer spending
is at an all time low.
[MAN 2B] Can't say
I blame them for saving.
Everyone's at
their wits' end.
[MAN 2A] But it's not just
Japan. Consumer spending is down
around the globe.
[IOGI] It makes you wonder if
it's still within our reach.
[SOICHIRO] Don't worry about
consumer spending. People may
be focused on saving now but
eventually, the tide will turn.
We simply have to
be patient, gentlemen.
I think that wraps up things
for today. Until next time.
[MAN 2B]
Very well.
[MAN 2A]
Goodnight.
[SOICHIRO]
Find anything?
[IOGI]
Yes, sir.
Nineteen-year-old Kimimaro
Yoga, a second-year student
at Heisei College
of Economics; has
a complicated family history but
otherwise he's quite mundane.
[SOICHIRO] He must be one of
those "middle of the road types"
who don't want
to draw attention.
He's gotta be
thoroughly confused right now.
[KIMIMARO]
Can I help you?
[HIGH SCHOOL GIRL 2A]
Just these.
What's this?
Sorry, you can't pay with this.
Wait what?
This's gotta be
play money, right?
No, it's a thousand yen.
What's your deal? You don't know
a thousand yen when you see it?
C'mon, quit messin' with me.
Excuse me, sir? But could we
please get a different cashier?
[KAKUTA] 238 out of a thousand.
Your change is 762 yen.
Would you ladies like a bag?
[HIGH SCHOOL GIRL 2A]
No thank you.
[KAKUTA]
Please come again!
If that was 'sposed to be
a joke, I'm not laughing.
No, just hold on a sec!
What does this look like?
Huh?
Just tell me!
A thousand yen.
Right. How 'bout this one?
It looks the same
as the other one.
Hold these, I need
to go to the bathroom.
Mashu, do you know
what's going on?
[MASHU] It's always been like
that, you just couldn't see it.
This may not be
a big deal to you
but I'm totally
freaking out here!
Why? It's just money.
Yeah, but it's creepy looking.
All the cash
in the District is black.
You're saying it's
just like regular money
once it makes its way
into this world?
Pretty much.
So it's okay to use it then.
Why're you asking me?
I'm no expert.
Hey!
Is something wrong, Mashu?
You're gonna have to decide
if you want to deal or not!
If you don't have
the will to fight,
this isn't gonna end well!
Look, I can't babysit
you forever, got it?
[yelping]
You've gotta start taking this
seriously! It's not some game!
Okay.
Better get going.
[SHIMADA]
Something wrong?
[KIMIMARO]
Nah. I'm fine.
Can I help you?
[MALE CUSTOMER 2A]
Just this. Don't need a bag.
All right, sir,
197 out of ten thousand.
That's 9,803 yen.
[MALE CUSTOMER 2A] You kiddin'
me? I saw a five thousand
yen bill in there! Gimme that.
No I can't.
[MALE CUSTOMER 2A] If I take
those small bills my wallet'll
be too fat
to fit in my pocket!
[KIMIMARO] It's just that that
bill is kinda dirty and--.
[MALE CUSTOMER 2A]
What the hell do I care?
Hand it over, you idiot!
[SHIMADA]
Sir, please calm down.
Stay outta this, old man!
[KIMIMARO]
What the hell are you doing?
[MALE CUSTOMER 2A] That how
you talk to your customers?
You want me
to call the manager?
Just gimme
the damn money already!
There's nothing wrong with it!
Here ya go.
Huh?
Shut your mouth,
take the money,
and get outta here
right now, 'kay?
[MALE CUSTOMER 2A] Who the
hell do you think you are?
[SOICHIRO] Is that enough
to persuade you?
[[MALE CUSTOMER 2A laughing]
Ain't no take-backs, man!
Fine. As long as I don't
have to look at your ugly face,
I would say that we're even.
[KIMIMARO]
Excuse me, sir?
Here, I wanted to thank you.
[SOICHIRO]
You bought me a coffee?
[KIMIMARO]
Yeah, but it's no big deal.
I ran into a little
extra money recently.
[laughing]
No hold on. I'm sorry.
I didn't mean to laugh.
Thank you.
[SOICHIRO] Must be tough working
at a convenience store
this late at night.
[KIMIMARO] It's not so bad.
I'm used to it.
But you're not used to
the black money, are you?
[KIMIMARO]
Hey. Who are you?
I'm just someone who happened
to see your first deal.
You're pretty impressive
for a rookie.
So then you've been
to that city, too?
[SOICHIRO] Only people who've
been to the Financial District
can tell the difference
between regular and black money.
Actually, it's called
"Midas Money".
'Cause it's issued
from the Bank of Midas.
[KIMIMARO]
Is it dangerous?
[SOICHIRO] No more than
regular cash. It may look
a little strange but there's
no harm in using it.
[KIMIMARO] I was told my future
is being held as collateral.
Is that true?
[SOICHIRO] Yeah, but the money
you borrow against it can help
build a better future.
[KIMIMARO] May I ask what
you do for a living?
[SOICHIRO] Now, that's a tough
one. I guess you might say
I use money. And exceptionally
large sums of it.
If things work out,
maybe you can do the same.
[chuckling] I couldn't care less
about being rich! All I want
is a normal life with
a guaranteed salary
and a family of my own!
And that's really
good enough for you?
Why wouldn't I be happy earning
a living like everybody else?
You're just gonna settle
for "normal"?
But that's no different
than running away
from a challenge.
You're not a coward, are you?
[KIMIMARO] No! Not that it's
any of your business.
Maybe you're just afraid
of losing. Is that it?
Your father
had that fear, too.
How would you know that?
If a comment like that
makes you mad, then you must be
trying to run away
from your parents as well.
[KIMIMARO]
Do you really know my dad?
[SOICHIRO]
You've gotta quit running.
Don't be afraid
of your own potential.
Everyone has to
find meaning in their life.
Thanks for the coffee.
[KIMIMARO] You're saying
I can't be normal?
[SOICHIRO]
We'll find out.
My name is Soichiro Mikuni.
And I would be willing
to help you. If you decide
to make something of yourself.
Either way, I'll be waiting,
on the other side.
[SATO]
Hmph.