♪ opening song ♪
[HANABI]
This is your third?
Let's go!
Oh, wow. I'd like
to have lots of kids someday.
You're so lucky!
Professor Ebara, since when--?
Going on a year and a half,
I think. The money I make here's
enough to take care of my family
in the real world.
My third child
is due any day now.
So I'm afraid
I can't go easy on you.
If you want kids,
don't wait! Just go for it!
What? There's no way
I could afford to have
a big family like yours!
It's still way too soon.
[EBARA'S CARD]
Poison Pill.
[KILL]
Yes sir!
You okay?
Poison, huh?
Don't worry about money,
it'll work out fine.
Trust me. We may be stretched
from time to time,
but we always get by.
Guess that's how it is
for everyone these days.
[TOSHIKO chuckling]
It isn't so bad.
I've perfected
my business model.
[EBARA'S CARD]
Direct.
[EBARA]
You don't stand a chance!
[MASHU]
Kimimaro!
[KIMIMARO choking]
[KIMIMARO'S CARD] Watch.
Watch. Watch. Watch. Watch.
You have to sell now! You have
to sell my stocks! Hurry!
[KIMIMARO'S CARD]
Yours.
Mashu is yours.
[SOICHIRO'S CARD]
Mine.
50 Million! Let's have it!
Well, I think I'd
better head home.
Thanks for stopping by.
I know it was a nuisance,
but I really needed you
for today's class.
[TOSHIKO] It's fine.
I could use some exercise.
Mezzoflation, hurry up!
[KIMIMARO'S CARD]
Scorched Earth.
[MASHU]
Scorched Earth!
That kills me every time!
It was fun.
[FEMALE STUDENTS]
Thanks for coming! Goodbye!
[FEMALE STUDENT 4A]
She was nice.
[FEMALE STUDENT 4B]
Yeah.
[KIMIMARO'S CARD]
You have gain.
[EBARA gasping]
[EBARA'S CARD]
You are bankrupt.
[EBARA]
That wasn't a fair deal.
Well, your opponent
didn't break any rules.
Then what the hell happened?
I was obviously winning!
Yes, you were winning,
but when a third party
bought stocks from
the losing Entre's Asset,
the situation turned
around quite quickly!
This was the result of
a commercial transaction,
that's all.
Bullshit! How dare--
Well, bovine feces aside,
you're still expelled.
Thanks for your time.
A pleasure
doing business with you!
What're stocks?
When you get an Asset, you get
ten stocks with them, too.
One belongs to you
and the other nine
can be traded for money.
[KIMIMARO]
Uh, thanks.
[SOICHIRO] I don't remember
doing you any favors.
I made a strategic investment,
that's all.
You just happened
to benefit from it.
[KIMIMARO] That may be.
You still saved me.
If you think about it
from your perspective,
that's true but that's not
exactly how I see it.
I made an investment
and do you know why?
Because you expect something
from me in return?
Sure, but it's
more complicated than that.
[SOICHIRO] It's true that I
stopped you from going bankrupt
but I also wanted
your Asset's stocks.
In other words,
we share a mutual interest.
That's why I say
there's no need to thank me.
Or I could've helped you out
just to be nice.
So maybe I'm not
such a bad guy after all?
Maybe.
[KIMIMARO] What happens
to the people who lose?
[ITANEDA]
Who knows?
It's different for every Entre,
so there's really no tellin'.
[KIMIMARO] My dad committed
suicide after he went bankrupt.
[ITANEDA] That's pretty common
after a loss. Guess they don't
want to be a burden on
their family and all that jazz.
Well losing him
was an even bigger burden.
But Professor Ebara,
I hope he doesn't
end up that way.
[ITANEDA] Think of it as one
more surprise waiting for ya
when you get back home!
[KIMIMARO] I'm an idiot
for even talking to you
in the first place.
[ITANEDA] With all the
negativity floatin' around,
you gotta find the positive
anywhere ya can kid.
[ISURUGI] We currently have
over twelve hundred members
which means we control
about thirty three percent
of the Financial District.
If we get to fifty percent,
we'll control the effect
this city has on the real world.
But we still have to
consider our opposition.
[SOICHIRO]
Forget about them.
There's no point
in forcing them to join.
All we need to do is wait.
When they see there's profit
in it, they'll come to us.
If they don't have a cause,
I s'pose they don't have
any other loyalties.
[SOICHIRO] The ideals of the
Starling Guild will change the
way the whole system operates.
Eventually our guild
and the Financial District
will be one and the same.
So does that mean we should
"forget about" that boy as well?
Him? We'll have
to wait and see.
[GENERAL CHATTER]
Good morning!
What are you looking at?
Oh nothing, really.
Just spacing out.
[SUBDUED CLASSROOM CHATTER]
Did you understand
last night's homework?
I know I'm usually
the one who pays attention,
but business administration
is boring.
Okay, let's pick up
where we left off.
Jeremy Bentham's
theory of utilitarianism.
[EBARA]
I know you're all excited.
[MALE NEWSCASTER 4A]
Their three-year-old son
also suffered major injuries
and he was rushed
to a nearby hospital,
where he died upon arrival.
There's been a lot of
accidents involving kids lately.
[KIMIMARO]
Yeah.
And just the other day
some boy died in a fire, too.
Poor little guy.
Such a terrible way to go.
Gotta run. I'll see you later.
[HANABI]
Huh? Wait what?
[KIMIMARO]
Professor Ebara!
I know I'm the last person
you wanna see but please
hear me out. I had no idea our
deal would end the way it did.
I'm sorry. I'm glad
to see you're all right.
I was really worried.
I don't know what I'd do
if something bad had happened.
I'd feel like it's my fault.
Uh, Yoga?
[KIMIMARO]
Yeah?
[EBARA]
Are you free this afternoon?
[KIMIMARO]
Yes, sir.
[EBARA] Why don't you
come by my house?
C.
[EBARA]
I'm home!
[TOSHIKO] Well, this is a
surprise. You get off early?
No, I've got a student
with me who needs some
private tutoring.
Say hello, Yoga.
Thanks for having me.
[TOSHIKO]
Oh, it's our pleasure!
[EBARA]
I don't know why I was chosen,
but one day Masakaki appeared
in my house and invited me
to the Financial District.
At first I didn't want
anything to do with it
but it wasn't long before
I was hooked.
It takes money
to raise children.
I was reluctant to have kids
because I knew we
couldn't afford it
but my wife
wanted to try anyway.
And I don't blame her.
She doesn't understand
financial burden because she
comes from a wealthy family.
I knew my salary wasn't
enough to support a child
but she wouldn't take
"no" for an answer.
The Financial District was
the solution to my problems.
It was thanks to
the money I earned in deals
that I was able
to start a family.
What is it that
you're fighting for, Yoga?
[KIMIMARO]
Good question. I don't know.
I'm still looking
for the answers myself.
[EBARA] You've been doing
some soul-searching?
[KIMIMARO]
I don't know.
[EBARA] Whoever said that
having something to fight for
makes you stronger was a liar.
If it was true, you never
could have defeated me.
[KIMIMARO] Well, I don't know
if I'd consider that a win.
And what does that mean?
It doesn't count as a win
just because
Mikuni bailed you out?
Take any advantage
you can get!
[EBARA]
Be proud of your victories.
Because when you lose
you're left with nothing!
It all crashes down!
My dad killed himself
when he went bankrupt.
He was an Entre, just like us.
[EBARA] I'm sorry. But I can
understand why he did it.
In fact, I've thought about
it myself. It's strange.
As an Entre, I was forced
to borrow against my future,
which the bank
is holding as collateral.
It was such
a nebulous concept
that I was willing
to hand it over
without even giving it
a second thought.
It wasn't until I went
bankrupt that I realized
how truly devastating
losing your future could be.
Sorry to interrupt, I thought
you might like some tea.
No, it's fine. You shouldn't
have gone to the trouble.
[KIMIMARO]
Did you have your baby?
What?
[KIMIMARO]
It's just, weren't you about
to have your third child?
[laughing] Now, you must be
confusing me with somebody else.
Oh thank you but, uh,
I thought you were--
[TOSHIKO] I swear there's
something in the water.
First you and now your student?
I think I would know
if I was pregnant.
We don't have kids.
It's just the two of us.
[TOSHIKO] Don't get me wrong,
I would love to have children.
Unfortunately, I haven't had
any luck conceiving.
[EBARA] It'll happen, honey,
there's no rush.
[TOSHIKO]
Sure, you say that now
but what about your
drunken rant last night?
I woke up to him yelling,
"Where are the children?
What happened to them?"
I thought you had
lost your mind!
[EBARA] No, that was just
the booze talking.
I don't know
what came over me.
[TOSHIKO] Maybe deep down
you do want kids.
[EBARA] No, no, I was just
dreaming, that's all.
It must've just been a dream.
[EBARA] When I returned,
everything had changed.
My children never existed.
Even the child in my wife's
belly disappeared.
There were no records,
no photographs.
Now all I have left--
--are memories of a family
that never was.
Our world has been changing
right before our very eyes.
The shifts are so subtle
most people never even notice.
But it's steadily
getting worse and worse.
I wonder what your father lost
when he went bankrupt.
After what happened to me,
I'd say you're lucky
to even be here right now.
I'm so sorry.
[KIMIMARO] All of this happened
'cause I won. It's my fault.
[EBARA] I admit, we wouldn't
be here if I hadn't lost
but think--If you
had lost the deal
it's highly likely that
you would've found yourself
in a similar situation.
Surely that's not
what you want.
There's no way
to win, is there?
Either I make
other people suffer
or I end up suffering myself.
What kind of choice is that?
This may sound pessimistic
but when it comes down to it,
life is about taking
what you want from others
and having things
taken from you. For example,
another man took Hanabi away
from you, isn't that right?
No. It isn't like that!
She's just--she's just a friend.
I think my point still stands.
[EBARA] If I had known things
were going to turn out this way,
I would've joined
the Starling Guild.
[KIMIMARO]
What's the Starling Guild?
[EBARA] You've never heard
of it? It's an organization
in the Financial District
run by Soichiro Mikuni.
He claims its purpose
is minimizing
the Financial District's
effects on our world
by controlling the amount
of money exchanged in deals.
It seems like quite a few Entres
have joined their ranks lately.
When you become a member
you give up any chance
of ever winning big but they
also keep you from going bust.
I tried to steer
clear of them, myself.
But if I had known then
what I know now,
I would've buddied up
to Mikuni real fast.
Just so you know,
I don't hold a grudge.
I don't blame you for anything.
I chose to participate,
and I take responsibility
for my actions.
If you want to make it up
to me, then don't lose!
It'd only make
this situation worse!
I want you safe because
you're the only other person
in this world who has
any memory of my children!
Hey Mr. Shimada,
how many kids do you have?
[SHIMADA stammering]
Where did that come?
I'm sorry I just realized
I've never asked you about them.
I see. Well that's all right.
I never really set
the record straight
on that one.
Now's as good a time
as ever, right?
I, uh, don't have any kids.
[KIMIMARO] Oh, so it's
just you and your wife?
No, just me.
Don't have a wife.
Never met
the right girl, I guess.
Maybe I shoulda tried harder
when I was young.
[SHIMADA chuckling] Sorry I
didn't mention it sooner.
Yeah. Not to pry but
don't you want to get married?
Even if I did, you really think
there's a woman out there
for a guy who's pushing
sixty and works
part-time nights
at a convenience store?
[Q] Listen. Can you hear
that creaking sound?
[SOICHIRO]
No, what is it?
It's the city.
It's creaking.
It's as though
it's reaching its limit.
I do what I can
and that's all, Q.
That's good enough for me.
The buildings creak when
they're tilted to the left
as well as when they are tilted
to the right. Therefore--
There is no right
or wrong way to tilt them.
I knew you'd
say something like that.
An Asset must'nt
disappoint her Entre.
[SOICHIRO]
This city will never fall.
We will never get
out of dealing.
Winning may be hell
but losing is even worse.
So, the way I see it, the only
choice is to keep winning.
But don't you ever
feel bad about it?
Not at all. Because
I've finally figured out
the proper way of doing things.
I don't understand.
[MASAKAKI] Mr. Mikuni,
please come with me.
It's time for your deal.
Watch, and I'll show you.
Uh, okay.
[HORII] Mr. Mikuni's deals
always draw a big crowd.
But they tend to be
pretty lavish productions
so that's no surprise.
It's one darkness card
against another, huh?
If you're that torn up,
why don't you just quit?
You don't have a lot of money
to lose so if you went bankrupt
now you wouldn't die. I mean,
your professor didn't, right?
Even if I don't die,
that doesn't mean
someone else won't disappear!
Well that settles it then!
That means no more
whining outta you,
ya got that?
Mr. Kikuchi.
If you might reconsider,
I'd still be honored
to have you in our guild.
[TAKEDAZAKI] Look at that! The
Syndicate's tagging along today.
In that case, pardon me for
making a bit of money off you.
[SOICHIRO'S CARD]
Open deal.
Kakazuzu.
Yes, sir!
Hurst, go!
[KIKUCHI'S CARD]
Pac-Man Defense.
This is nuts.
[MASHU]
Check out the balance sheet!
He's losing money but it's
going down at a steady rate!
It may seem like
he's losing ground but
he's in total control. I gotta
admit, this guy's not half bad!
[TAKEDAZAKI] Hurst is a powerful
Asset but its maintenance cost
is too high.
At this rate of earning,
Kikuchi is going to lose.
Open my stocks to the public!
[KIKUCHI'S CARD]
Yours.
Hurst is yours.
Alright!
I'm buyin'!
Me too!
[KIKUCHI] Now I can take
my time and enjoy this.
[SHINDO]
The Syndicate, huh?
[ISURUGI] Mr. Mikuni has
15 billion,100 million
but after selling his stocks,
Kikuchi has double that
at 36 billion, 900 million.
[KIKUCHI] Let's see how long
you can fend me off, boy!
[MASHU] It's decreasing
at the same rate as before.
Now!
[SOICHIRO'S CARD]
Direct.
Check, Old Man.
You can't keep this up.
The backlash from
his Pac-Man Defense
can be a real bitch,
you know!
You're too cocky
for your own good, boy.
[KIKUCHI] Time's almost up.
Looks like I win.
Smooth as silk.
He isn't off by a single yen.
You had enough fun for today?
What was that?
[SOICHIRO]
White Knight.
[SOICHIRO'S CARD]
Another one!
Man here she comes!
Alright, Princess. Hurry.
She found the core?
[shrieking]
[SOICHIRO thinking]
Will she make it in time?
[SOICHIRO]
Princess, come back, quick!
And now I think I'll have you
give me back my money, old man.
[KIKUCHI] Your money?
Your money, you bastard!
[SOICHIRO'S CARD]
Direct.
[KIKUCHI yelling]
Mikuni!
[SLEEPING BEAUTY]
You need your sleep, remember?
[SOICHIRO'S CARD]
Closing.
[KIKUCHI'S CARD]
You lost.
[SOICHIRO'S CARD]
You have gain.
[MASHU]
I can't believe it!
He won! By only one percent!
You do realize that even
one percent can have an effect.
Congratulations on your win.
Thanks.
That was really great.
So you say, but you don't look
all that impressed to me.
Seriously, I thought
you were amazing out there
and I'm being honest.
But that doesn't mean I want
you to take me under your wing.
'Cause I don't have
any interest
in becoming
a powerhouse Entre like you.
Okay then what do you
want to become?
[KIMIMARO]
I'm not sure.
[MASHU]
Annoying, isn't he?
[SOICHIRO] That old man is
strong. It's because he has
a huge amount of money
backing his Asset.
If I made him go bankrupt
it would have a huge effect
on the real world.
That's why I couldn't
let that happen.
Deals aren't about
winning or losing.
The real thrill
comes from making
the maximum amount of profit
without taking too much away
from your opponent.
After all you have to consider
what influence
that flow of money
will have on the real world.
That's why I have
to be as strong as I am.
[KIMIMARO] Then all I have
to do is not lose, right?
[SOICHIRO] Yeah, but first
you have to be strong enough
to control that.
[KIMIMARO]
I'll try. No, I'll do it.
I've had enough. I don't want to
rob anyone else of their future.