According to Mr. Barkin of
the FRB, if the US dollar is
allowed to grow any weaker--
The American market's
finally started to move.
If we get pressured
by a strong dollar,
foreign currencies are gonna
collapse across the board.
So America thinks they can stop
C's chain reaction if they can
throw enough of their money
into foreign economies?
In addition, the IMF will
be providing relief--
That guy is an American Entre.
The one on the left.
You kiddin' me?
America's entire history
has been shaped
by the Financial District.
While foreign investors from
around the world have rushed
to support them, entire nations
have disappeared as collateral.
Hell's bells! You may be
handsome, but you play dirty.
We can't help but throw cash
around. North America has lots
of super duper entrepreneurs!
But you can have this!
The North American Financial
District was able to repel C!
It's headed straight
back to Japan!
The one that took Singapore's
about to hit us again, huh?
Then it's time for round two.
You think we can
protect ourselves?
Well, look who it is!
Get the rotary press
moving again.
And make it snappy, alright?
But of course, sir! Though
I must warn you we'll be
taking additional collateral.
I trust you don't mind?
Mikuni.
Due to America's
intervention in the market,
currencies all around the
world are collapsing.
To protect this country
from "C"s chain reaction,
Mikuni's used the rotary
press a second time.
The rotary press?
It prints all the Midas Money
in the Financial District,
using the country's
future as collateral.
Wait. Is that the reason
stuff keeps disappearing?
That idiot. I never thought
he'd use the damn thing twice.
Is there any way to stop it?
Not personally, since you
need a Darkness Card
to enter it in the first place.
Thanks to Kikuchi's
fight with Seizawa,
Mikuni's the only one left
in our District who has one.
So there's nothing we can do?
There's one thing we could try.
The last time Mikuni
used the rotary press,
there was a several hour
grace period between getting
the Midas money and
when the future was lost.
You saw it yourself.
Yeah.
That's our only chance
to make a stand.
We'll have to put in a bid for
a deal and then bankrupt him.
If that works, we'll get his
Darkness Card and have a chance
to run the rotary press in
reverse to put back the money
back to the bank before our
future is taken as collateral.
But do you think we can beat
Mr. Mikuni in a deal?
The source of his power is his
wealth; which means it has
the same weaknesses
as any other currency.
In other words, it can be worth
a lot or nothing at all.
When I'm done, it won't be worth
the paper it's printed on.
What are you gonna do?
That's the question, huh.
I'm gonna use every trick
in the book to make the value
of the yen hit rock bottom.
And since Mikuni's precious
Midas Money gets its strength
from the yen, if my plan works,
his mighty fortune
will be mighty useless
in no time flat.
It's a simple fact.
Money derives all its power
from confidence.
Get it? Undermine that
confidence, and the rest
takes care of itself.
You might say we're starting
an economic domino effect
with confidence as a catalyst.
The pieces will keep falling
down, one after another.
The final domino will be
the Financial District.
Everything depends on
what we can pull off
during our
"grace period". Yoga?
Yeah.
It'll all be over if the
guild members interfere.
I'm counting on you
to hold them up.
Okay.
It might sound dramatic,
but this deal is our chance
to win the future back.
If we do this, no one else
will disappear, right?
I'm just an asset, if I get
wiped out, it's no big deal.
So don't wuss out on this!
I know. If we sacrifice
the future,
then what are we living for?
Whatever! I get it! You don't
need to get all philosophical
on me all of a sudden.
I know what I want
to protect now.
I'm ready to fight for real.
Good, so no more
speeches, okay?
Hope this isn't
too much for him!
By the way, have you
caught the rat yet?
I've got him by the tail.
Little bastard's been trapped
by his own scheme.
Alley oop! The transfer
you requested is complete!
PIN code?
Confirmed.
Here it comes.
This is enough to buy a small
country! Mikuni and Sato are
too charitable for their own
good. Why waste all their
hard earned money on
the ignorant masses?
What the hell?
Give it up, You think
you're sly, but Mikuni's
been onto you for a long time.
You always got on my nerves.
You and your polka dot ties.
Nice doing business with you!
You were a red herring from
the start, Mr. Isurugi,
but you left a nice little
crack in Mikuni's defenses.
Alas, I can't say I'm
too sad to see you go.
Sinners who play saint leave
a bad taste in my mouth.
Helicopter money, drop!
Would you like
to choose an opponent?
Yes.
What! A hundred million yen!?
The yen is useless!
Exchange it for dollars!
Yes! Yes!
Mr. Mikuni?
What is it?
You have a request for a deal.
Tell 'em I pass. C's chain
reaction is closing in.
Very well. But I must remind
you, if you wish to pass,
you are required pay
half of your total fortune.
Is this a joke?
I'm sure you'd rather
our future trying
to fight that chain reaction,
but there's nothing you can do.
A dog from the IMF.
This must mean you're
trying to stall me,
what're you cooking up now?
The details don't matter. I want
a deal and I'm getting one.
Isn't that right, Masakaki?
Indeed. Like it or not,
I'm afraid rules are rules.
You say I'm just trying to
stall you, huh. Of course,
you automatically assume
that you're going to win.
What kind of arrogant ass thinks
he can save an entire country
on his own? You have no
right to spend our future-
it doesn't belong to you!
You think this is arrogance?
Your opponent, Mr. Horii,
is already waiting for you.
So you were just hanging out
with us for kicks, huh?
If Mr. Mikuni couldn't win you
over, I won't bother trying
to change your mind.
And besides, it's not like
I'm gonna turn down
a deal when it's staring me
right in the face.
I'll warn you, though.
I'm strong. This won't be easy.
Hey, Masakaki.
What is it my boy?
Mashu's been
acting strange lately.
Never fear- it's quite normal
for an asset to experience pain
while the rotary
press is running.
But I thought assets
weren't able to get hurt!
As you know, an asset is the
future of the entrepreneur.
The very future that
is now being siphoned
and turned into money.
So. It's only logical that they
would be affected adversely.
Don't worry, I'm alright.
I'm ready to do this!
You really are tough,
aren't you?
You don't have to force
yourself, okay? Just relax.
I'll handle this.
I'm your asset. If you're gonna
fight, then I'm fighting too!
As my asset, it's your job
to do what I say, Mashu.
I don't have to win.
All I have to do is hold out
'til Ms. Sato can get
the Darkness Card.
Don't be stupid!
Direct.
You're gonna fight me on your
own? It's your funeral, pal.
Open deal.
Insider!
Sucks to be you, traitor,
I'm gonna make this hurt!
Damn it.
You can't do this alone!
I'll be all right.
Kimimaro! You have to let
me out! You gotta let me
fight with you!
No way.
Insider on! So long, sucker!
Let me help you, please!
Hold on, something's wrong!
Damn it! What happened!?
Don't bail out on me now,
you piece of junk!
Ah, that hurt!
Why do you care so much
about the future, anyway?!
You don't know if it'll
be good or bad or what.
It's not worth killing
yourself over! Is it?!
Mashu.
No matter what happens.
I'm glad I met you.
C'mon, pal.
Don't leave me hanging here!
Insider.
You know why
the future's important?
Because you are
my future, Mashu.
Damn it!
Insi-Insider.
I may not know what it holds
for me, and maybe it's silly
to risk my life
to protect something
I don't know anything about.
But even if I can't see the
future, I can still see you
and I want to protect you.
Isn't that the same thing?
Get up and move already!
Oh, so now you decide
to work? Blade!
Y'know, you can be
a real pain in the ass,
but there's nobody
in the world I like better.
What's that supposed to mean?
I'll protect you!
Ready for round two, huh?
I'm gonna rip you to shreds!
Let's hit him with a Macro!
Invest everything
and I'll barbeque him!
Micro, Mezzo, Macroflation.
Overheated Economy.
If this doesn't do it,
nothing will.
I don't believe it!
Why couldn't I see that coming?
Is it 'cause
my future's really dying?
This is nuts.
Closing. You are bankrupt.
You have gain.
Hey!
I guess using a Macro
takes a lot out of me.
We'll just have
to use 'em sparingly.
Why are you such a weirdo?
Excuse me for being concerned.
You okay?!
I don't wanna leave you
yet, Kimimaro. After all,
I know you're
hopeless without me.
I'll buy it back. Our future.
C.
Now, let's see here.
Might be time to put
the next step
into action, huh?
Hello, Takedazaki speaking.
This is the Fuji Times, right?
I've got some
exclusive information
if you're interested in buying.
This is gonna
rock your socks off.
Open deal. Micro,
Mezzo, Macroflation.
Mergers and Acquisitions.
You're gonna be flat broke
when I'm done with you!
What the hell?!
Kakazuzu, go!
As you wish.
Micro.
Aurora, go!
György! Hang in there!
Direct.
Q. I dunno if I'm gonna make it.
Micro, Mezzo, Macroflation.
Mergers and Acquisitions.
You're mine!
Looks like twice is the limit.
I'm not finished yet!
EBO. Direct.
That's impossible! How can
your asset enter on its own?
Cannibalization.
Direct.
I know my hands are stained with
blood, but I chose this path.
I walk it without regret.
You smell like you'd make
a nice snack.
I hear the government
accidentally gave out
millions of yen 'cause
of some machine error.
That's why you
gotta spend it now!
That's right, spend
it all, 'cause soon,
you won't even wanna
wipe your ass with it!
Rapid inflation!
Hyper inflation!
--banning the exchange of yen
to foreign currencies.
Similarly, there is also
a ban on the depositing
of foreign currency as well
as sending cash or checks--
Alright. I wonder which is gonna
disappear first: this country,
or the Bank of Midas!
I guess that'll depend on how
well Ms. Sato's holding up.
Are you there?
Ms. Sato, are you okay?
I'm sorry, but there's no
way I can turn this around.
Mikuni's stronger
than I thought.
I don't stand a chance.
I did all I could do.
If you know there's
no way you're gonna win
why don't you
withdraw from the deal?
Sorry, asshole,
but that's too easy.
I'll be a thorn
in your side 'til I die.
You really are a bitch,
aren't you?
I guess I can't
disagree with you.
Yoga, I'm sorry
I got you wrapped up in this.
But I have to ask
for one more favor.
I can't look after
György anymore. Take him.
He's my future,
take good care of him.
Go!
György is yours.
Thank you, and good luck.
Watch, watch, watch.
Mine.
You are bankrupt.
I don't know what you planned
to do but Sato already failed
to take my Darkness card.
If you were trying to stop
the press, then give up.
One of my co-workers disappeared
right in front of my eyes.
What's your point?
And it isn't just him kids
are disappearing too.
'Cause of you! It's happening
'cause you started the press!
You can't tell me that's
right, sacrificing the future
to protect the present.
Don't you realize how much
the assets are suffering!?
Q is your future, isn't she!?
Don't you feel anything!?
Don't you care!?
If Q disappeared
because of what I did,
then I would disappear with her.
I can't concern myself
with the consequences.
I won't accept that. I was
wrong to ever believe in you.
There's no way
I'll let Mashu disappear.
I'm gonna protect my future!
Mikuni!
What's wrong?
Our account was emptied out
and given away.
So that's their plan?
Using my own money
to destroy the economy
with hyperinflation.
When the value of the yen
drops, then Midas Money,
and all of my assets,
will become weaker, as well.
We can't defend
against the chain reaction now.
Don't lose your head!
Go back to Japan
and contact
the defense fund recipients.
I'll prepare the money.
I'll get right on it, sir.
Hey, Masakaki!
How may I assist you?
Start up the rotary press
one more time!
Are you sure?
If you aren't careful,
you'll burn through
your entire future.
I don't care! Start it!
You've already
done enough damage!
If you destroy the future,
what's left to fight for!?
Scream all you want,
so long as you're weak,
it won't do any good.
To realize your ideals,
above all else, you need power.
You're going to
have to accept that.
I won't let you do it!
Won't let me? You're in no
position for threats, Yoga.
Please don't despair, Mr. Yoga.
Why, if I'm not mistaken,
you have a Darkness card
as well, don't you?
My goodness Mr. Mikuni,
do you see that?
Whatever shall we do now?
With that card, Mr. Yoga
can reverse the direction
of the rotary press.
You son of a bitch!
What the hell are
you' trying to pull?
Me? I'm innocent,
I assure you! I don't decide
on these sorts of things.
I follow my orders from above!
Do it! Spin the rotary press
in reverse!
You think I'll just sit back
and let you win this?
You're going to have
to get through me first.
So be it.
Then the deal is on, gents!