Tell me, Soichiro. What is this?
Well, it's money, sir.
Choose your words carefully.
I'll ask again.
I don't know, Father.
It just looks like money.
Not "Father"!
Call me "Mr. Mikuni."
Yes, Mr. Mikuni. I'm sorry.
"My sincerest apologies, sir."
I told you to choose
your words carefully.
In business, people will
take advantage of you
if you make even
the slightest error.
As you observed, this is money.
That's clear enough.
But watch. When I
pile it up like this,
it becomes something
more than money.
Do you understand?
This is power.
Wherever you go, it is the only
thing that moves this world.
Pure power.
Right after I
graduated college.
I became my father's
executive assistant.
You don't have to do anything,
just sit back, observe,
and think very carefully about
what I'm doing. And learn.
I'm not going to
stop and explain
every little point to you.
Yes, sir.
My band in college
had a record deal,
but we had a fight and broke
up before we could sign it.
The whole experience ruined my
passion for music. In the end,
that's probably why I finally
gave in to my father's wishes.
In a nutshell, my father's job
was to build business networks.
He exchanged money upfront
and behind the scenes alike.
With money, he formed powerful
bonds with powerful men.
If one side collapsed,
both would go bust.
So in the midst of a crisis,
they'd rush
to each other's aid.
That is the meaning
of power. Of course,
my father isn't the one who
created the system. He simply
made a place for himself in a
world that'd existed for ages.
Well, how do you like your job?
I'm getting by.
You know, I'm not so sure you're
cut out for the business world.
You don't think so?
So, are you really
quitting music for good?
If you're a businessman
or a rock star.
You're still just working
to make a living.
I guess, but your music
wasn't all that bad,
if you ask me, at least.
I didn't think you'd give up
on it so soon, that's all.
Gimme a break. It may sound
harsh, but there aren't
many people who can actually
survive off of their dreams.
Frankly, I'm not one of them.
So, if my dreams
won't pay the bills,
I'll live off the shit
reality feeds me.
I see.
My father tried to hammer
everything he knew into my head.
He wanted to keep the business
in the family. The rest
of the office didn't care for
me, but that hardly mattered.
You told me she had stabilized!
That was true at the time,
but she's taken
a turn for the worse.
What? Don't give me that crap!
Then, would you rather I lie
to make you feel better?
There was no hospital in
Japan that could save
my little sister. She
needed to be taken to
a specialized
facility in America.
It was expensive and the
arrangements were complicated
but I tried to make it happen
as quickly as possible.
But then suddenly.
All of a sudden,
everyone is selling!
How am I supposed to
explain this to our clients?!
At this rate,
we're gonna go bankrupt!
Mr. Mikuni! Is there a plan?
The company was sinking.
It was a fragile system
The empire my father
had built hinged
on other networks' intervention.
We can sell some property,
if the situation's that bad.
I have an image to maintain-
who would want to do business
with a man who
had lost his house?
Just thought-
The only thing we need
right now is confidence.
No matter what others say
we must retain our composure.
We cannot panic.
We cannot be unnerved.
We must put on
a brave face at all times.
Lose your head
at a time like this
and your future
is soon to follow.
I understand.
I've canceled Takako's
visit to the U.S.
What did you say?!
I simply can't
afford it right now.
Can't afford it!? You're gonna
let your own daughter die
just to save a few yen?!
There's no guarantee that she'd
be saved in the first place
I don't need a guarantee! It's
still worth a shot, isn't it?!
Face it. The writing's been
on the wall for a long time.
What does that mean!?
You're just giving up!?
Even if Takako dies,
people won't
lose confidence in the company.
What kind of father are you!?
I may be your father, but before
that, I am a public figure!
There are certain
things I must uphold
even if it comes at
the cost of my own family!
Someday, you'll understand.
What makes you think I'll
end up like you?! If you're
not willing to save
your own daughter's life,
I'll come up with
the money myself!
It didn't make any sense to me.
I didn't care if the business
was failing. What kind
of monster would sit back
and watch his own child die?!
I could never forgive him.
Go inside. Mr. Mikuni
gave me instructions
not to let you leave.
I don't give a damn; you have no
right to stop me! Now get lost!
Please forgive me.
After that, I was under house
arrest for days. Apparently,
if clients saw me running
around trying to raise money,
confidence in the company
would drop. If you ask me,
that would've been a small price
to pay. But what could I do?
I was powerless.
You had better
go see your sister.
What happened?
Would you please leave
the two of us alone?
It's been a while.
I've missed you.
I'm sorry
I thought that maybe I wouldn't
be able to see you again.
Takako.
They said with the way I am
now, I wouldn't be able
to get to America anyway.
But actually,
I'm a little relieved.
Because I didn't wanna
leave Japan.
Why not!?
I don't expect you to
understand what you probably
take for granted,
but when you go to sleep,
you know tomorrow will come.
And after this week,
the next will come.
After this month passes,
And after this year
will come the next.
But for me it's not like that.
When I go to sleep tonight.
I know I might not
wake up tomorrow.
So for me, the only thing
that matters is
this moment right now.
Instead of forcing me
to go to another country.
I'd rather stay here with you.
I know, you probably think
I'm silly for feeling this way.
It's alright.
I really wish today could last
forever. And I don't even care
if I never get better.
So long as tomorrow will be
the same as today.
That night,
Takako slipped into a coma.
To this day,
she hasn't woken up.
I closed my heart
and buried myself in work.
My relationship with my father
was limited strictly
to business.
Before long, I was visited
by a strange man.
Good evening.
I accepted his offer.
I asked him why
he hadn't shown up before
when I had needed help.
If only this had
happened sooner,
Takako might've gotten help.
Sorry, I wish I could help you,
but I'm in no position
to answer that.
It may not seem like it, but
this city has a will of its own.
It trifles with our fates.
It mocks each of us.
I can feel it looking down upon
me, and sneering, laughing.
Well, if it wants to toy with
me, then I'll be to return
the favor. I'll bend
its rules. I'll make it
play my game and use it
to protect the real world.
I don't care about being rich.
I don't care about their system.
All I care about
is getting my way.
Something troubling you?
Just lost in thought,
that's all.
It's nothing to do with us.
C.
Kimimaro! Kimimaro!
My Entre's a real weirdo-
I can't figure him out.
I was disappointed
when I first met him.
He seemed kinda
slow in the head.
And when the deal started,
I think he got dumber
and more useless than before.
Also, when he has to do
one thing but wants to do
something else, he ends
up doing nothing at all.
And when he's
in trouble he doesn't
look at things logically,
he just follows his feelings
Angel.
You're the only thing
that matters to me.
I can't lose you. I won't lose
another person I care about.
C'mon, let's go.
Our last battle was
the toughest yet
but somehow we pulled through.
Thing is, when he saw what
happened to the guy we beat,
he got all depressed again.
I have no idea what
I'm supposed to do anymore.
Just fight.
Well yeah, I know that much.
Then why're you
still moping around for?
'Cause I feel like it.
Just give me some time. Man.
He never can make up his mind.
And when he does he wonders
if he made the right choice.
There isn't anyone else
like him in the whole city.
Assets are technically
their Entre's property.
So everyone tends to have kinda
a businesslike relationship.
But he's different.
He doesn't see it that way.
At first I figured it was
because I look like a human.
But I think it must
be something more than that.
So, you're supposed
to represent my future, right?
Yeah.
Then can you tell me
what's gonna happen to me?
I dunno.
They say when an Entre's future
is taken as collateral,
their Asset becomes
the embodiment of that future,
Well, that's what
everyone says, at least.
But I don't think anyone
really knows how it works.
When is it going to be
the future for him
and what does that mean
for me? Will I change?
It doesn't make sense.
We assets have nothing
to do with the future.
We only exist to fight in deals.
For us, there is no future.
I never had a problem with that,
but now I'm not so sure.
Lately, whenever he's
worried about something,
it makes me worry, too.
Does it really
bug you that much?
The future.
Well yeah, I don't know
anything about it.
I'm sure the future's important,
but like Mr. Mikuni said,
so is the present. You don't
think about that stuff?
Not really.
It'd probably matter
more to you if you
lived in the real
world like me.
If all you do is worry,
I think I'm better off here.
Thanks to my weird partner,
things never get boring.
Is that right?
Even though it's more fun this
way, things would probably be
a lot easier on him if we
acted like other Entres.
Let's get some dinner!
I thought you said assets
don't need to eat anything.
Yeah, but I gotta see if those
are as good as your ramen!
Wait a second!
Evidently Humans need to take
in what they call "nutrients"
every day. Otherwise they'll
run out of energy and die.
Oh, hey, kid. I hear you've
been raking it in
since our last deal.
I keep trying to break even.
Oh, I joined the Starling
Guild a while back.
Did you?
I don't think I'm cut out
for that kinda stuff, myself.
It's a lot less trouble
working alone.
I know. It's tougher
than I thought.
If you know,
then why'd you join?
Well, 'cause at first, I didn't
think it would be all that hard.
Don't worry.
Easier said than done.
You got Lady Luck
on your side, after all
Sure. Anyway. There's a question
I wanted to ask you.
Sure, shoot.
Assets are supposed to be
the physical embodiment
of their Entre's future,
aren't they?
But your asset is a giant
monster. Do you ever wonder
what that might mean
about your future?
Who knows? I've got no idea
why Gyiyg looks like that.
Lemme know if you figure it out.
I always wondered.
You too, huh?
I guess all Entres worry about
what their futures are like.
What's the big deal? I'm me.
Isn't that good enough?
Come on! It's good! Try it!
It might make you stronger
for your next deal! Look
how much that other asset
is eating!
Listen man, those things
are almost human.
Don't just feed it.
Think of it like a girlfriend.
You gotta do all kinds
of stuff to keep it happy.
Girlfriend, huh? More like
a pet. If you eat your food,
I'll give you a treat.
Don't let 'em get to you.
There's still a lot I don't
understand about him.
What's wrong?
Nothing.
Then stop staring.
But there is one thing that I
know for sure. Even if he gets
on my nerves sometimes,
I like being with him.
I mean, sure, he's always
doing stupid stuff,
but that's what
makes him so much fun.
I've had enough.
I can't keep running away.
I've never been able to
make decisions 'cause
I'm too afraid. I'm scared that
if I make the wrong choice
everyone'll be
disappointed in me.
But that's just an excuse, isn't
it? What I'm really afraid of
is getting hurt myself.
I'm a coward.
I keep running away
instead of taking action.
I waste my time
worrying about what to do
and I end up doing nothing.
That hurt. What the hell is your
problem, you little shit!?
How do you like it?!
Why'd you go back to hit him?
'Cause I didn't wanna
end up doing nothing.
The way those guys were
talking really pissed me off.
I wasn't sure fighting them
was the right choice.
But when I decided not
to do it. I felt ashamed.
At least fighting them is better
than doing nothing.
But starting a fight
with some thugs isn't smart.
So even though I finally made a
decision, there's still no way
to know for sure if
I made the right one.
I still don't get it.
Maybe Mr. Mikuni and that Sato
lady expect a lot outta him
because he's willing to do
crazy stuff sometimes.
Prepare yourself!
Wow! What a deal!
Cloudy skies with
a 10% chance of--
today's horoscope!
If you're a Leo--
Go back a little.
Yeah! What are they doing?
They're kissing.
Kissing? What's that?
When two people like each other,
they put their lips together
and it's called a "kiss".
I wanna try it!
Whoa, not so fast!
You can't just kiss anybody!
You have to really
really like the person!
Is that how you do it?
Look, whatever you're
feeling, it has to be like
30 times stronger
or it won't work!
Man, what a let-down. Then,
can you at least tell me
what it feels like?
I, uh. I wouldn't know.
I've never done it.
I see.
So if you've never kissed
anybody, does that mean
you don't know
what it feels like?
Nope.
If you liked me, and I liked you
30 times more than I do now,
you and I could kiss?
Well, sure,
when you put it that way.
Okay! I'll try
to like you more, then.
All right. Be my guest.
There's a lot of things
I still don't understand,
but it's fun figuring them out.
I never know what
she's going to do next.
The future sure is full
of surprises, isn't it?
Maybe I've been
worrying too much.
The future will work
itself out somehow.
Hey.
Yes, sir?
There used to be five
skyscrapers over there,
but now there's only three.
Did they get torn down?
Beats me. I'm too old to keep up
with all that crap.
I don't know why. But everything
looks a little different
than it did before.
Sure it's not your imagination?
Not that it matters either way.
Whatever it is, it's gone.
Best off forgetting it
for our own sake.