After the shock of the Southeast
Asian Financial crisis,
Economists speculated
that the stock market
might begin picking up.
Their hopes were dashed when
trillions of yen were
mysteriously deposited
into bank accounts
across the country
causing the value of the
yen to drop dramatically.
3,000 yen to the dollar?!
You're trying to
rob me blind, aren't you?
Go ahead and exchange it!
Stores won't
take anything else!
So the current decline of the
yen has nothing to do with "C"?
No sir. It's some sort
of conspiracy.
But, what about "C"?
Take a look at the screen.
Oh, honestly.
I can't believe that
the people of this world
can be so simple-minded.
I've had a feeling
this time would come.
And I did as well, Q.
It must be fate.
No, it's necessity.
Deep down I've always known
I'd have to
face off against him.
Wouldn't you consider
that to be fate?
I suppose you have a point.
You ready?
Yeah.
You've got one hour
until it's time to "settle up"!
Open deal!
Princess!
Sleeping Beauty Microflation.
'Kay Mashu. Micro, 50 million!
One billion!
Direct.
Watch out!
Let's switch out, Mashu!
Swap.
Let's try a mezzo.
EBO. Direct.
What do you mean I can't
exchange my money?!
Apparently every country
around the globe
has ceased trading in yen, sir.
I never thought I'd see
the day Japan's currency
would be null and void.
We're going to have to
prepare for the worst.
Direct. Direct.
Shame it had to come to this.
Q!
Now switch it up!
Swap.
Talk about playin' with fire!
When it's dicey
in the real world,
it's sure to be the same here!
Oh, it's dicey all right.
Unfortunately,
you were the one I chose
to carry the torch after me.
No matter what happens
to me or when,
I want to make
this moment last forever.
After getting to know you,
I'd thought we both
shared that belief.
You must not "know"
me that well.
Although we may not
be able to see eye to eye.
We want the same end result. I'm
afraid that doesn't matter now.
Kimimaro, you have to
use a Macro!
No. That's way too strong.
I don't want to.
You have to go all out!
I'm telling you,
that's the only way!
Micro, Mezzo, Macroflation.
Q.
Economic Blockade.
Here goes.
Overheated Economy.
I can't move!
The FSA has issued a nationwide
ban on currency exchange.
Financial institutions
have closed their doors
causing angry citizens
to start rioting.
If your little sister was
a victim of time like mine.
I'm sure you would want to stay
in the present as much as I do!
Direct.
That's not what your sister
wanted and you know it!
You're stuck in the present
'cause it's what you want!
You said you wanted to protect
the present to save the future,
but you were just satisfying
your own selfish desires!
You've never walked in my shoes
so how the hell would you know?!
What?!
You only take dollars?!
You can't be serious!
C'mon, that stuff about
the yen was just a rumor!
I'm sorry but that's
our store policy, ma'am.
We've received orders
from headquarters
not to accept any
Japanese yen whatsoever.
I can move again!
'Kay, then let's
charge one billion!
Micro, Mezzoflation.
Okay!
What's the matter with you?!
Why can't you understand?
We are our Entres' futures!
I thought I was the one
fighting for Kimimaro,
but it turns out, he's the one
putting his life on the line
for me!
Don't you think there's
something wrong with that?!
I couldn't care less.
Well, I think you should care!
Like I care about Kimimaro.
And I could lose him
because of you!
Do you know what my sister's
last words to me were?
She said, "I wish this day
would last forever". She said
"I wish these unchanging days
would last for eternity"!
So that's the way it's going
to be! My sister doesn't even
understand the concept
of "tomorrow"!
That's why it's so important for
me to keep the present alive!
As far as I'm concerned,
you should be taking care
of the people who are
right in front of you.
Not worrying about people
who may or may not
be a part of your future!
You bastard. This is all
'cause of you! Damn it!
I wanted to take care of the
"people right in front of me"
but they changed
because of you!
If I hadn't acted we would've
fallen victim to "C"!
Lives were spared because
of my actions! I saved them!
If they don't have a future,
then why did you
even bother saving them?
If she were here now,
your sister would be heartbroken
that her words caused this.
And she would tell you
that you're wrong!
He intends only his own gain,
and he is in this---
Did you see the Prime Minister's
press conference?
Yeah, it was amusing
watching the government
try to cover their tracks.
They've lost all credibility.
Are you planning
to leave Japan?
If I was smart I would've
left a long time ago.
Mr. Mikuni has a sister,
and he says she can't wake up!
Why, you! Scorched Earth!
Cannibalization.
Micro, Mezzo, Macroflation.
Scorched Earth!
Economic Blockade.
Cannibalization.
What's wrong?
I just realized. You have
the same face as his sister!
Shut your mouth.
You are his sister, aren't
you? Does he know?!
You have to tell him!
He's sucking the life
out of everyone so he can
try to keep you alive!
Why should I listen
to what you have to say?
Because, I happen to care
about my Entre!
Are you still talking?!
I don't wanna be separated from
him but I keep fighting anyway.
I've chosen to do
it for his sake!
Why are you fighting?
For Mr. Mikuni's sake?
But why would you
when you can't be sure
he's doing the same for you?
Shut up! Shut up! Shut up!
What's the deal?!There's fake
money mixed in with my change!
No way.
You'd better take back
this black paper
and give me some
real change right now!
C.
There isn't anything you can do!
Neither of us can stop it!
The fall of the human
race is inevitable!
You never know
which day may be your last.
That's why I choose to live
each one to the fullest!
I don't give a damn
about tomorrow because
the only thing you can
depend on is today!
But what happens when you
make it through another day
and it's worse
than the one before?!
Then that becomes
my new standard!
Q. Eat up! I want you
to devour this Entre!
Q?
Takako.
Direct.
'Bout time to wake up
from the dream, gentlemen.
C's chain reaction.
It's headed straight for Japan!
What the?!
I'll make you pay
for what you've done!
You feel okay, Big brother?
Yeah, I'm sorry sis,
I'm just a little tired.
I think you should
take a break.
You've been fighting
awfully hard.
I can't now--
The way you've
been acting lately reminds me
a lot of Father.
I'm sure that he had
something he wanted to protect.
Just like someone else I know.
I remind you
of our old man, huh?
Yeah, okay, I get the point.
It's crazy to think I've ended
up just like the one person
I didn't want to become.
Takako? Takako? Takako!
Takako.
The chain reaction passed
through without incident.
I didn't think
that was even possible!
Midas money is now as
worthless as the Japanese yen
it supports. Uninterested
in our valueless currency,
"C" passed us right by.
Soon this District
will cease to exist.
I know you're in
the middle of a deal
but I'm afraid we don't
have much time.
Kimimaro wins. He beat me.
Are you sure?
What would you
like to do, Mr. Yoga?
You know what I want. Spin
the Rotary Press in reverse!
You may regret doing this.
But I won't stop you.
Your wish is my command.
This is it. I'm gonna
buy back the future!
Here we go!
You have control.
I guess this is goodbye. Q.
I'm sorry I stopped fighting
so abruptly. But I realized
continuing would
not benefit you.
It's time for you to start
a new life without me.
I wish I could stay by your side
for all of eternity, Soichiro.
I know, I do too,
but you have to go, Q.
No, Takako.
This mean we won?
Sure does. Thanks, Mashu.
The big goodbye. Sucks, huh?
Yeah, it does.
30 times, right?
Say what?
That's what you told me.
Right now, I think I might love
you 40 times more than usual.
Really?
Oh, Kimimaro,
I'm so glad that I met you.
Mashu! Me too!
Take care of yourself.
We'll meet again
in the future.
I don't think so, kid.
I've decided to stay
in the present forever.
So pretty!
I know I may annoy people when
I rant about the importance
of consumer confidence.
But I'm pretty sure
what happened to the
Financial District today
helped me proved my point!
I don't wanna sound cocky
but I single-handedly
tore the place down and now
I'm riding off into the sunset.
I wouldn't start
celebrating just yet.
You're not ridin' off into the
sunset more like oblivion.
Guess you relied
on the District
more than
you thought ya did, huh?
Just when I think I'm out,
they pull me back in.
A lotta good all that "consumer
confidence" crap did for ya.
I can't keep up
with the capriciousness
of this country any longer!
Where am I?
You debated both options,
trying to decide which
was right and wrong, but there's
something I should tell you.
Both options are correct.
There is no single answer.
Your views of the future may
have differed but your goal
was the same. You fought to
make the world a better place.
Then what was the purpose
of the District?
It was created to bring you
all together and to help you
find that common goal.
It served its purpose.
I realize it may seem to
bring about evil and tragedy,
but in actuality it was designed
to help guide the human race.
Promise you won't forget
what you learned.
Who are you?
You're hardly going
to recognize the world
you're about to revisit.
Each of you will be returning
with something precious.
You're lucky to be able
to take it back.
You must never forget that.
That'll be seven dollars
and thirty cents.
Thank you very much,
ma'am. Have a nice day!
Let's go, hurry up!
C'mon, mom!
Calm down, Nori!
Don't run too far ahead.
Let's try to stay
with the group.
No running off on your own.
Is everyone following me
like good boys and girls?
--Hey Hanabi-
--Teacher!
What is it?
Look! There's
a doggy over there!
A doggy! Where?
Oh, isn't it cute!
You see a nursery school
teacher who looks like
the girl you have feelings
for, and you can't help
but to ask yourself, "Could this
be my doing? Is it possible
she's living her felicitous
future because of my actions?!"
And just as you're filled
with emotion I show up
and burst your bubble.
Pardon me.
Is this a joke?
I'm as serious
as a heart attack.
What are you doing here?!
Surely you didn't think
you'd get rid of me that easily.
As you know, this is the future
you took back. In our eyes,
it will always be collateral.
Therefore, wherever
the future exists so do we.
The Financial District
is eternal, my boy.
That can't be.
No need to worry.
I won't be bothering you.
There are plenty
of prime-quality futures here.
They'd be perfect
for collateral!
Of course, you're welcome to
give me a shout anytime. 'Kay?
'Til we meet again!
I should've been smiling.
For the future.