[alarm sounds]
[MAKITA] Damn it.
This one doesn't work either!
[ATM 1A] Please take
your card and try again.
[alarm sounds]
We are unable to process
your transaction at this time.
Please take your
card and try again.
[MAKITA] Huh?
[alarm sounds]
[MAKITA gasps]
[ATM 1A] Thank you for
choosing Tokyo Hogoraka Bank.
[MAKITA] Huh?
[ATM 1A] One moment please.
[MIDAS ATM ] Pin code?
Please enter your pin code.
Confirmed.
Do you want to make a deal?
[MAKITA]
Yes. Yes, I do.
[MIDAS ATM] Would you like
to choose an opponent?
[MAKITA] Yes.
[car engine accelerates]
[car door closes]
[ITANEDA]
Where ya headed, buddy?
[MAKITA] The Financial
District. Step on it.
[tires screech]
I had a feeling you'd say that.
[MAN'S VOICE] He intends
only his own gain and he...
[SOICHIRO] Look around.
You may be able to find a few...
...who realize the truth.
But there will always be others.
Those who simply
can't understand.
Some suspect it, of course.
Others choose to be oblivious.
But the simple fact remains.
In the end, money is money.
Its value is subjective.
One moment it's precious.
Then in the blink of an eye...
it's completely worthless.
Q!
Do you have anything to add?
No, as long as I can eat
my fill, I am satisfied.
Heh. That's simple enough.
[Q]
I don't understand.
Do you not find it simple?
[SOICHIRO]
Not necessarily.
But I don't find it
complicated either.
As your position changes,
so does your perception
of its value.
Money is a curious thing.
Dealing with it is
like a game of chance.
A game that I personally
have tied to the
"real world" as well.
Everyone's a player.
But very few people actually
realize what's going on.
The rest are
completely clueless.
Even among people who have
spent time in this world.
Few of them truly
understand the concept.
Mr. Mikuni, I hate to interrupt
such a rousing soliloquy
but it's time to go.
[SOICHIRO] Masakaki.
Wait, I thought that deal
was going through tomorrow?
Due to circumstances
beyond my control,
I was forced to move it up.
I'm on a date, does
it have to be tonight?
I'm afraid so, but your
lady friend can come along.
So, who's my opponent?
[MASAKAKI]
Why don't you see for yourself?
He's right over there.
This your first deal?
Yeah.
A rookie won't last long
against a player like me.
[MAKITA] Haven't you ever
heard of beginner's luck?
[SOICHIRO]
You're gonna need it.
[KAKAZUZU]
What a fool.
[MAKITA'S CARD]
Direct.
In this world,
anything's possible!
[SOICHIRO'S CARD]
Open Deal!
[MAKITA yells]
If you were looking to gamble,
you should've dealt with
those guys, not me.
I didn't come here to gamble,
I'm fighting you because
I need the money!
Heh... Yeah?
[HACHIONNA screams]
Well, so do I.
[SOICHIRO'S CARD]
Direct.
[MAKITA grunts]
[MAKITA screams]
[EBARA] So we have
product A and product B.
Now the owner of A
wants to trade it for B.
That doesn't necessarily
mean the owner of product B
wants to trade for A, right?
What makes this situation
difficult is the fact that
neither A nor B
has a set value.
So, how do we go
about establishing
the worth of these products?
Believe it or not,
this is exactly how the concept
of currency was brought to life.
[HANABI] Kimimaro.
[KIMIMARO]
Oh. Hey, Hanabi.
I don't understand why you're
studying for the civil service
exam when you haven't
even finished college yet.
I wanna pass so
I've gotta study.
Practical learning's
more important.
College classes bore me.
[HANABI]
Concentrate on graduating
or you won't be able
to find a job,
let alone become
a civil servant.
[DUDE 1A] Hey Yoga!
Party tomorrow night! You just
gotta chip in for booze.
[KIMIMARO] Yeah. Sorry guys,
I've already got plans.
Are you comin'?
Yeah, I don't know.
I'll have to think about it.
If you don't have
the cash, I'll cover you.
No way. I don't want charity.
[DUDE 1B] He's been
rollin' in dough lately.
I don't know if
I'd say rollin'.
[DUDE 1B] Business must've
really picked up for your
old man's company, huh?
[KIMIMARO]
I've gotta get to work.
Oh! Wait a sec. Hey!
I've got notes for
the big test... tomorrow.
Geez, that guy's
seriously antisocial.
Yeah, no joke.
[ATM 1B] One moment. Your
transaction is being processed.
Please don't forget to
take your withdrawal.
[KIMIMARO]
Chip in for booze...
[ATM 1B]
Please don't forget to...
Yeah, like I can afford that.
♪ opening song ♪
[TRAIN ANNOUNCER 1A]
If you are standing,
please hold on to
the hand straps.
The next station--
[STATION ANNOUNCER 1A]
May I have your attention;
a train will soon be passing
through the station
on track number 3.
For your safety, please
stay behind the yellow line
as the train passes through.
Caution: a train is now...
[thud]
[PASSENGERS gasp]
[confused chatter]
[PASSENGER]
Ah! What's going on?
[confused chatter]
[PASSENGER]
Now I'm gonna be late!
[KAKUTA] You sure you
wanna be a civil servant?
Well, I'm not gonna work
in the private sector
with the way things are now.
But it isn't like civil servants
have job security either.
Nobody's safe.
Yeah, I guess you're
right about that.
I just feel like my
odds would be better.
I guess they might be.
[KIMIMARO] All I want is to
have a family and to be able to
provide for them with
a guaranteed salary.
I don't think that's
too much to ask.
Livin' thriftily
with a wife and kid.
Sounds pretty frickin'
humble to me.
[KIMIMARO] I can't keep
slaving away like this.
Oh crap. Looks like
I'm gonna be late.
Just leave that stuff.
I'll take care of it for ya.
[KIMIMARO] Thanks a lot, man.
I'll see ya later!
Have a good one.
[SHIMADA]
That's impressive!
You're a full-time student and
you have two part-time jobs?
[KIMIMARO ] The other
convenience store I work for
couldn't give me
any more shifts.
[SHIMADA]
Ah, to be young again.
[KIMIMARO]
I work hard
but it's nothing compared
to guys like you
who work to support
their families.
[SHIMADA laughs nervously]
Is that your friend?
[KIMIMARO] Huh? Uh...
That's Hanabi.
You do know there's
a test tomorrow.
[KIMIMARO] No way! This is
the first I've heard.
Is it a pop quiz?
[HANABI]
You're gonna need these.
I wrote down all the
main points for you.
Just read 'em over before you
go to sleep and you'll do fine.
Thanks a lot.
But you shouldn't have gone
out of your way like this.
My life would be easier
if you'd get a cell phone.
Then I could just
text the notes to you.
[KIMIMARO] Yeah, I would
but I can't afford it.
I'm flat broke right now.
[HANABI] I don't want
to sound rude, but
I get the feeling you have
money you just don't spend it.
[KIMIMARO]
I like being self-sufficient
so I have to be careful with it.
[HANABI] Was that a dig at
those of us whose parents
pay for our college education?
[KIMIMARO]
No, I didn't mean it like that.
If you keep obsessing
about living a "normal" life
it'll end up being anything but,
and that'd be totally lame.
You came all this
way just for me?
Mm-Hmm...
So, don't say I never do
nice things for you, okay?
My shift's almost over,
what do you say I take you
to dinner to say thank you?
[HANABI]
My boyfriend's waiting for me.
Sorry.
[KIMIMARO] Uh, no problem.
Guess I'll see you at school.
You'd better ace that test!
I'll try!
[door closes and locks]
[KIMIMARO dryly]
Honey, I'm home.
[KIMIMARO sighs]
It gets pretty
lonely around here.
It sucks you're gone but
I kinda like living alone.
I don't have to worry about
'causing problems for anybody.
Oh--! So much for that.
Hanabi totally went
out of her way for me.
[knocking]
[yawning]
[dog barks in distance]
It's night already?
[MASAKAKI] Good evening.
I'm a representative
from the Bank of Midas.
My name's Masakaki.
Do you have a moment?
Huh?
[whispering]
[MASHU] C.
Who are you?
Masakai from the Bank of Midas.
I'd like to talk to you
about fund management.
[KIMIMARO] No thanks man,
I'm not interested.
Look, I don't have
any money, okay?
[MASAKAKI]
Just hear me out.
My offer might surprise you.
I may be able to help you start
earning money more efficiently.
In fact, you could easily
double or triple your income.
[KIMIMARO] Uh... I'm sorry.
But I'm not really interested.
[MASAKAKI]
Are you sure?
[KIMIMARO]
Just get outta here.
[door slams and locks]
Talk about pushy. Huh?
I keep studying but none
of this stuff is sticking.
Huh?
[MASAKAKI]
Have a seat.
Huh?
[MASAKAKI] I've brought
you to a place where time,
as you know it, does not exist.
I suppose you could
think of it as limbo!
But you don't have
to stay here forever,
I'll send you back
when you're done studying.
Go ahead--have at it!
Huh?
You've barely said more than
"huh" to me this entire time.
Uh... uh...
[MASAKAKI] We have an
opening for an Entrepreneur
in the Far Eastern part of
Asia's Financial District.
We desperately need
to fill this position
so we've randomly chosen--
Well, guess who?
Kimimaro Yoga, a student at the
Heisei College of Economics.
That is you, isn't it?
Uh, yeah.
[MASAKAKI] You see,
the Financial District
is open to almost anyone.
No special skills
required. Lucky for you.
The first time you visit you
may feel a tad overwhelmed
but there's no
need to be afraid.
You'll get the hang of it.
[KIMIMARO] Yeah.
Now you keep saying "yeah."
Is that really all
you have to say?
Yeah.
[MASAKAKI]
Fine, have it your way.
But you'll have to gather
your wits sooner or later.
[KIMIMARO] Is that supposed
to be some kinda joke?
If anybody needs to "gather
their wits" around here,
it's you!
No need to be cruel,
I'm trying to prepare
you for your new role.
Oh yeah, and what
"role" is that?
Ta-da! You have been chosen
to become an Entrepreneur!
An Entrepreneur?
Sorry, I don't have a clue
what you're talking about.
You're an Entre! That's what
we call them for short.
Sounds cool, don't you think?
Yeah, that's great...
But I still have no idea
what you're telling me.
[MASAKAKI] I'm afraid you're
going to find the concept
hard to grasp.
Graduates of our
educational system
are virtually incapable
of abstract thought.
[KIMIMARO]
Are you calling me stupid?
[MASAKAKI chuckles]
Ahh!
[MASAKAKI] How can I put it
in terms you'll understand?
All that you have to
do is simply agree to
tender your future to us.
At that point, we'll
hold it as collateral
and you'll be able to
borrow money against it.
[KIMIMARO] Huh?
We'd like for you to
start investing in
the Financial District and
we'll reward you with money.
Is that too much to ask?
You want me to
give you my future?
Technically, it's still yours.
But it might change,
depending on your actions.
So this could take
years off my life?
Well, that's the chance
you take with this deal.
Then forget about it.
I don't understand.
Don't you want money?
Of course I do.
But I'm not willing to
risk my future for it.
But you could afford
to go to the party.
You wouldn't have to
work two part-time jobs.
And you could enjoy
a stable lifestyle
without ever having to fight
to become a civil servant.
How'd you know that stuff?
You're intrigued, aren't you?
Be honest.
Ah!
[MASAKAKI chuckles]
Whoa.
What a dream...
[beeping]
What the--?
One, ten, hundred, thousand,
ten-thousand, hundred-thousand?
So, how'd you do on the test?
[KIMIMARO]
Uh. Okay, I think.
Thanks for the notes,
they really helped.
You're not as "self-sufficient"
as you thought, huh?
[KIMIMARO]
Heh... Guess not.
[DUDE 1B] Yo!
[DUDE 1A] We may have to
cancel the party tonight
'cause no one can chip in.
It's not like alcohol's
that expensive.
If it happens, my offer
still stands, Hanabi.
[HANABI] Thanks but I don't
know if I can make it.
I think I'm in.
[DUDES gasp]
[DUDE 1A]
Whoa dude, are you serious?
[DUDE 1B] Cool, I guess
we'll see ya tonight then.
[KAKUTA] I'd spend it.
It's their mistake, right?
Besides, it's not like you
stole the money or anything.
Well no, but still.
[KAKUTA] It'd be one thing
if it was 10 million yen
but it's just 500 thousand.
[KIMIMARO sighs]
You're stressin' out
for nothin', man.
[SHIMADA]
Hypothetically speaking?
That's right. What would you
do if it happened to you?
[SHIMADA]
Back when I was your age,
I would've reported
the mistake to the bank.
No kidding, right?
[KIMIMARO laughs]
[SHIMADA]
But at this point in my life,
I'd probably go ahead
and use the money.
Having extra cash is
always a good thing.
And the bank won't
miss 500 thousand yen.
Besides, if you were to
report it, it's possible
someone could lose their
job over a silly mistake.
[KIMIMARO]
You've got a point.
[SHIMADA]
Everybody needs money nowadays.
I mean, take a look at me.
You think I enjoy working
at a convenience store
all hours of the
night at my age?
[KIMIMARO] Maybe if I just
take out a little bit.
[ATM 1C] Please don't forget
to take your withdrawal.
[alarm sounds]
[KIMIMARO grunts]
[MASAKAKI]
Well, look who's here.
I knew it wouldn't be long.
At the end of the day,
it all comes down to money.
Wouldn't you like the
opportunity to make more of it?
If all goes well, you can
have anything you desire.
Even that girl's heart.
Hanabi isn't the kinda
girl who'd date a guy
just 'cause he has money!
[MASAKAKI] Oh really? Then
how do you explain the fact
that her boyfriend's
a spoiled brat?
As far as I can tell,
the only difference
between the two of you
is that he happens to
come from a wealthy family.
[KIMIMARO] You. You put
that money in my account?
[MASAKAKI]
I'm afraid it's the only way
I could get your attention.
That 500 thousand yen
is earnest money
and it's yours if you want it.
[KIMIMARO]
I think I'm gonna throw up.
[MASAKAKI] So what will you do,
my friend? Will you keep it?
Or shall I take it back?
Here's something
for you to ponder.
If your father had money, do you
think he might've stuck around?
What do you know about my dad?
[MASAKAKI] I know that
if you have the funds,
you may be able to find
out what happened to him.
[KIMIMARO]
Quit messin' with me!
[MASAKAKI] This is an invitation
to the Financial District.
Those with cards are granted
passage into the realm
without exception.
With this card you can withdraw
cash from any ATM in the world.
Please be careful with it.
Remember, we're holding
your future as collateral.
[KIMIMARO gasps]
[MASAKAKI]
Come with me.
Kimimaro.
You won't regret this.
I promise.
[ITANEDA]
Where to?
[MASAKAKI]
The Financial District.
Whatever you say, boss.
[KIMIMARO yells]
♪ closing song ♪