♪ opening song ♪
What? Is your guild
full of cowards?
Why don't you get over here
and fight me already! Curie!
I'm ready.
That's dangerous!
Lacking amount.
As usual,
I get horrible mileage.
Probably better to end this.
Mezzo! Insider-on!
Insider.
Microflation.
Move it!
Bastard!
Direct.
Right on the shoulder, please.
That kinda hurt.
Closing. You have gain.
All according to plan.
Yeah, let me see what you got.
Trojan Horse.
That's one hell of a growth rate
you have there. Bel!
Mezzoflation.
As you wish.
Dead Man's Trigger.
21% Mezzo, got it?
Yes, sir.
Breyer!
Closing. You have gain.
To minimize the effect
on reality, we win by
the slightest margin
possible. Our objective
is to control the deal so
we have to be acutely aware
of all the factors involved.
You mean like gathering
information on your opponent?
Well, everyone does that
sort of thing. But, for us,
it's more important to have
a grasp of our own strength,
over that of our opponent's.
That way we can more
accurately measure ourselves
against the other Entres.
Measuring my own strength?
Not just your
physical capabilities
but your intelligence,
wealth, and everything else.
The wider the criteria and
the wider your knowledge
the more accurate your
perception of your opponents
will be.
Their Assets too?
Absolutely. After all,
if we're measuring your strength
in a deal then your Assets
are the most important factor.
If that's the case, tell me more
about them before my next deal.
If you wanna know more
about Assets,
you have one
standing right here!
I didn't think of that.
You got a plan this time?
I hear this guy uses
a bunch of different attacks.
So I'm gonna try to
lay back until I figure out
everything he can do.
'Nother jackass from the guild?
This is gonna be a pain.
This would be a lot easier if
we just beat him down instead.
Work with me here.
I'm trying to figure out
how to control the deal.
Why'd I have to get stuck
with a weirdo like you?
Assets belong to their
Entres, you know?
So I can't put out a single
Micro without you're okay.
I know you're worried
but sometimes
you just gotta go
with your gut.
"Go with your gut"?
Open Deal.
Look at the time.
Today's membership dues
should come in any minute now.
Barbarossa!
Great Wall.
Microflation.
Micro.
Kimimaro!
What the hell is this?
Can you get out?
Hold on a sec!
This wall's not the Asset,
it's a flation?
Well aren't you clever!
So much for goin' with my gut.
What's going on?
Microflation.
All right, Barbarossa.
He's all yours.
Direct.
Take this!
You got out!
Get out of here!
Uh, 'kay!
Direct. Direct.
Damn it! Mashu!
Microflation.
Right!
Direct.
Barbarossa,
c'mere and protect me!
All we gotta do
is run down the clock!
2 million, 400 thousand!
Mashu, I need cover!
Direct.
No problem! You want
a flation, right?
No, just guard me!
You got balls, kid!
Bring it on!
Direct.
I almost had you. Damn it!
Perfect! It's close,
but I'll win.
Oh no, she's gonna ruin it!
Back off, Mashu!
Aww man.
Closing. You lost.
Aww... This sucks.
Well, what do you expect
from me in return?
As Deputy Governor,
I want you to stop
all budget cuts
for the next fiscal year.
You think the economy
could still use a boost?
Heh. I can't disagree with that.
However, the nation's up to
its eyeballs in debt and
something has to budge.
Don't worry, I'll continue
to cover the deficit, myself.
So the debt of our entire nation
would rest on your shoulders.
Frankly, I don't know
if I should laugh or cry.
Surely that man wasn't
serious-- who was he?
Oh, he was serious. When he
says he can bear the burden
of our debt, then we would
do well to believe him.
Without his help, our economy
would be unsustainable.
Sir, is this a joke? Even if
he could shoulder the debt,
why would he bother?
To help the people, that's why.
All that money?
Just to keep a couple
of public service programs open
while the economy
is falling apart?
Is that foolish to you?
Sacrificing yourself
to help the public?
Uh no, of course not.
No longer somebody
else's problem, is it?
You worry about what'll happen
to the poor saps you beat,
then it happens to you!
I didn't lose by much,
it shouldn't be a big deal.
Maybe, but I've seen
people's houses burn down
over no big deal.
What? But why?
Who knows? Guess it depends
on the bank and how much
of your future they wanna cash
in. It's kind of a gray area,
if you ask me.
Well, it didn't burn down.
Hello?
Hey, it's me,
just calling to check on you.
Talk about impeccable timing.
I was just about to leave
for the hospital.
There's no need to worry,
it's just appendicitis.
I should be home in a week.
You don't have to come visit me.
I'd be embarrassed if everyone
made a big deal out of this.
Whatever you say,
Aunt Kyoko. You sure there's not
something else? Nothing
bad happened recently?
No, why? I know I'm about
to be hospitalized,
but I'm in great shape
for my age.
That's good.
Did you see that?
Somebody actually failed!
Are you serious? I skipped half
the lectures and still did fine!
What can I say,
some of those guys out there
are a lost cause.
This must be the effect.
Well, guess that's not so bad.
What about Hanabi?
What's up with you? You look
like you've seen a ghost.
I'm fine. Nothing bad has
happened to you lately, has it?
Like an injury or an illness
or something like that?
Calm down. Nothing's wrong,
okay? I'm doing fine.
Actually, something
good just came up!
Remember that student
teaching application I sent
to my alma mater? It got
approved! It seemed like
there were a lot
of applicants this year
so I was kinda worried
but I was really
hoping that I'd get to go
back to my old school.
I have a lot of nice memories of
the place. Oh that reminds me!
I bought a new suit for the job.
Maybe I'll wear it next time.
You won't even recognize me!
My bad luck must not
have any effect on her.
Why am I so depressed?
I should be happy.
Congratulations on
surviving another week.
Right back at you. I'm glad
to see you could make it here.
Sadly, reality is being
rewritten same way as usual.
Birth rates and
resources are down,
while crime and suicide are up.
Sure spoils your day,
doesn't it? Whole world
getting switched around
behind your back.
Are your people
gonna do anything about it?
We don't have a plan yet.
We're not even
an international organization.
But on the upside,
at least they believe the info
you leaked to us is credible.
Here's what I have on
the Financial District.
Might not be anything new,
but I felt guilty about
taking and never
giving anything back.
See ya.
What?
I was wondering how you were
doing, with the injury and all.
Injury? That was nothing.
I know, I know, you're
a really fast healer, right?
All of this is your fault.
We were totally winning
that fight! Why'd you
have to stop me? Huh?
I was trying to--
You can't just pull that
crap outta nowhere!
How would you like it
if you got punched
and couldn't fight back?
I may heal fast but that was
still painful! If you have
some complicated battle plan,
tell me about it first!
But you probably just made
it up as you went along,
didn't you? Assets can only do
what their Entres tell them.
Huh? What's that beeping?
Oh. Sorry, I just made
a cup of ramen.
Cup of "ramen"?
Guess you guys don't have it
in the District. It's food.
Okay? So what's food?
Uh. It's the stuff you eat.
What does that mean?
You can't be serious.
You've never eaten a meal?
"A meal"? Nope,
I've never heard of a meal.
Okay. Here, lemme show you.
Oh my gosh that's
gross! Why would you
do something
disgusting like that?
For nutrition.
It gives me energy.
That, and it tastes good.
What does that mean?
Huh. How can I say this?
It just puts me in a good mood.
Kinda like when I'm having fun
or I'm happy about something.
Let me try some.
Come on. You said
it was fun, right?
Well, yeah.
Put it in my mouth. Here.
Nah, forget it.
Why not?
I'll bring some next time.
Hey! Stop that! Game over! Come
on you jerk! Save some for me!
C.
That's the guy
Mr. Mikuni fought last time.
His opponent is
Seizawa Yasushi,
another incredibly
wealthy Entre.
With that much money
to throw around,
they're gonna rip
each other to shreds.
No matter which one
of them loses,
reality is going to suffer
tremendously for it.
If only Kikuchi would show
the same restraint
that Mikuni showed him.
The old man is too stubborn
to think that way.
This deal is gonna
be a massacre.
If the guild doesn't take over
soon, we're all screwed.
Why weren't you
able to persuade him?
Gimme a break, the guy
is filthy, stinkin', rich.
He's not exactly
easy to bribe, you know?
We can get you the money.
No matter what the cost,
we can't let
deals like this go on.
Roger.
Open deal.
Here we go!
Pac-Man Defense.
The old fool only knows one
trick! Now, Porte! Mezzoflation!
Gatekeeper.
Mezzo already?
I'm about to bleed you dry.
Do you hear me?
I won't finish him off
at this rate!
Direct.
Basho Pharmaceutical's
stock took a dive today
as the company was rocked by a
number of serious allegations.
Their president, Yoshiki
Kikuchi, is faced with
several charges of embezzlement
and illegal drug sale.
With consumer trust plummeting,
the future of the company
is anybody's guess.
It's hard to imagine
that one deal could have
such a negative
effect on reality.
What'll happen if
Basho Pharmaceuticals
goes out of business?
Good question. It'd likely
start a chain reaction
of bankruptcies. We'd be looking
at economic losses upwards of
100 billion yen.
The company's assets
and any drugs they have in
development would be sold
to the highest bidder
to alleviate the debt,
which would be a huge loss.
What worries me is everything
I've mentioned is just
the tip of the iceberg. If Basho
Pharmaceuticals goes under,
their entire workforce will
suddenly find themselves
without work.
They currently employ
about ten thousand people.
The bankruptcy wouldn't
just affect Kikuchi.
It would effectively ruin his
employees' futures as well.
10,000 people.
Finally sinking in, is it?
Yeah. So, I didn't see
your wife. How's she doing?
I wouldn't know. She left me.
You'd think I'd be
broken up about it
but I don't feel
anything anymore.
Every day it gets harder
to remember my wife and kids.
Guess my memories are fading.
It won't work.
Why you say that?
'Cause there's no way
you can pull off these moves.
What does that mean?
It means your plan sucks
because you still don't know
how to measure
your own strength.
Back to the drawing board.
Like the guy said-- you
gotta know a bunch of stuff
if you wanna control a deal.
If you go in unprepared,
not only are you
gonna lose money,
I'm gonna get my ass whupped!
Fine, give it here.
Feeding your Asset, huh?
Now there's something
you don't see every day.
Is there
something wrong with that?
You can do
whatever you want, newb.
"Newb"? Did you come here
to make fun of me?
No, of course not.
I came here to sell you
some information
you might find interesting.
You know about
Basho Pharmaceuticals, right?
Of course I do.
You're worried about them,
aren't you?
How the hell do you know that?
I'm an information trafficker.
How about a cool million?
Isn't that kinda high?
Actually, that's
the minimum I charge
for my services
these days. So be grateful.
Besides, with the money
you're pulling in now,
that won't exactly
break the bank.
You'll probably hear about this
on the news in the other world
a few days from now. But FE
Pharma, a drug company formed
five years ago, just bought
out Basho Pharmaceuticals,
debts and all.
As far as the media
is concerned FE Pharma
is a foreign company but
in actuality the owner
is none other than
Soichiro Mikuni.
That means the damage
done to the real world
by Kikuchi's last deal
will be minimal.
That's the information
you wanted to hear, isn't it?
Did you need something?
Kind of.
That's Takedazaki for you.
But he's right.
FE Pharma does belong to me.
When Isurugi told me
that Kikuchi lost his deal
I took action right away.
Because you wanted to limit the
effect it would have on reality?
Exactly.
One of the Guild's purposes
is to combine our Midas money
to limit the damage the deals,
like that, might cause.
Eventually,
our guild will take over
the entire Financial District.
That'll make it easier
to control what happens
in and outside of the deals.
Why'd you take all this
on yourself?
Would you rather do it
instead of me?
What're you talking about?
So how do you like the city?
The Financial District, I mean.
What do you think?
Uh, I like it.
It's an amazing place.
Well, I can't argue with that.
I used to feel the same way.
But what's so amazing about it?
Uh, I don't know how to put it.
It's like this whole new world
with all these possibilities
that I never knew about before.
I suppose you could call it
a new world. But I always
thought of it as a mirror that
shows us a part of our world
that we never knew existed.
And that's pretty amazing, too.
It seems strange at first,
even frightening, the way
everyone spends Midas money. How
they can affect the real world
without even realizing it.
I thought, "Isn't there
something I can do?
Midas money is obviously evil!"
But then I realized something.
The Financial District
and Midas money are both
a reality we can't escape.
In the end, we could no sooner
destroy the Financial District
than we could destroy
our own world.
It's the same with Midas
Money. Trying to stop it
from flowing into our reality
would be like trying to stop
the circulation of all
currency on the planet.
Our only choice is to coexist.
But to make sure
that coexistence is
a relatively peaceful one,
I formed the Starling Guild.
All I can do is try to control
the profit-making balance
between our reality and
the Financial District.
So I buy Japanese government
bonds with Midas money
to prevent the
collapse of the country.
Even though you think
money's evil?
Our nation already moves
to the beat of its drum.
If the flow were to stop,
everything would fall apart;
everyone would be miserable.
Who would benefit
from something like that?
Even if the world is stained in
evil, as long as it's peaceful,
I'd still choose that over
a world where people starve.
I don't care if I get
my hands dirty. My only goal
is to protect this world
as it is now.
I understand that but
I still can't get used to
people using the black money.
I don't care if it's
the only thing
keeping our country
from collapsing.
I'm still not willing
to accept it, not yet anyway.
Just give it a little more time.
Someday you'll understand.
I'm not so sure.
I am. Trust me.
Hey, can I ask you somethin'?
Sure. Go ahead.
Why are you so interested
in that Yoga kid?
It's not like he's especially
sharp, just the opposite even.
And you said he was an
economics student, didn't you?
You sure wouldn't guess that by
the way he talks about money.
Those obsessed with money
hold onto it, they don't
make it move. That's what
makes him interesting.
For now, think of him as my
little pet project. Objections?
Nope.
Q, d'you hear that Kimimaro
fed his Asset instant ramen?
What's "ramen"?
If you'd like, I could
bring you some next time.
No thank you, I'm fine.
I read your report.
I hate to say it,
but it seems like
every time you come in,
the little bit of good
news we have turns bad.
It's not getting any better.
The Financial District
is destroying the
future of mankind.
You've made that point
abundantly clear.
We don't have time
to worry about the risk,
we have to stop the flow
of Midas money immediately!
I'm afraid that's not your
decision. Let me assure you,
you're not the only investigator
who's mentioned this.
I'm sorry, but you're just
a small-time bureaucrat
and there are some things you
don't have the power to fix.
This morning,
Kimimaro Yoga officially
became a member
of the Starling Guild.
Considering how he did last
time, isn't it a bit early
for a balanced deal?
Especially against that weirdo.
If he can't handle this, let him
crash and burn. Better now when
he won't cause a big
ripple in the real world.
Ugh! That's gross!
Open Deal.