[clock ticking]
[WOMAN]
Mage?
[door opening]
[WOMAN]
Did you have a bad dream?
I'm sorry, I...
I didn't mean to doze off.
[WOMAN]
It's all right.
But look, isn't it time
for your appointment?
Yes, it sure is.
[WOMAN] You should hurry.
He'll be waiting for you.
Oh, don't worry.
He always comes late, anyway!
[gasps]
[ticking]
[DERRIDA]
I'm going home.
To the place and the time...
...that saw this disaster
set into motion.
[ticking]
[MALE NEWSCASTER]
With the issue still unresolved,
the government has
declared another meeting
to be held tomorrow at the
emergency operations center
to discuss whether, on the basis
of the countries'
alliance agreement,
it should send
emergency aid and relief.
[FEMALE ANNOUNCER]
Welcome to a reinvented world.
--Serving--
--[DERRIDA] Erase.
Status on my appointment
with Jacques Yvain?
[FEMALE ANNOUNCER]
No reply has been received.
[DERRIDA growls]
Of course it hasn't.
[MAN A]
Derrida! Morning.
Hey.
[DERRIDA]
Morning, Nathan!
Remind me, what kind of
flower does Mage like again?
Come on. Tuberoses.
[DERRIDA]
Right, I knew that.
Anyway, when does her
birthday party start tonight?
Derrida, today.
You're going to talk
to your father, right?
[ANDREI]
There's no way.
It's the truth, Andrei!
We found an incredibly
dangerous bug
in the DZ's
underlying programming.
Go back 10 minutes
and delete the recording.
Now get out of here.
[ANDREI]
We have a duty here at Rebuild.
In the seven years since
the first Automata
went on the market,
human society has
come to rely heavily
on the autonomous robots
that our company provides.
And we've had almost
zero recalls in that time.
The DZ is on a totally different
level than previous models.
I'm sure you saw
the simulation data
that we attached
to our report, sir.
I don't recall.
I never bother reading reports
with imprecise data.
Look. If enough DZs,
like tens of thousands,
were given a joint
mission simultaneously,
there's a chance
that they'd go haywire
and become uncontrollable!
We just can't ignore this!
[ANDREI]
Tens of thousands of DZs
all getting the same order
at the same time?
Don't you find that
highly improbable?
[DERRIDA]
Not in combat.
If they're intended
for the front lines,
like I've heard they are, then--
[ANDREI]
You shut your mouth right now!
We can fix this!
We're developing
a corrected program!
If we can have them recalled,
and just get them patched,
we can avoid any further--
Enough!
Do you even understand what
you're suggesting here?
[ANDREI sighs]
Derrida...
Everything we've been building
culminates with the DZ.
Your father devoted half
his life to this project.
But, maybe that's it.
Maybe you want to
tarnish his legacy
by publicizing this minor flaw.
--[DERRIDA] That's not why...
--[ANDREI] I've heard whispers
you're jealous of
Jacques's accomplishments,
and you're plotting sabotage.
I didn't want to
believe them, of course--
Please, sir. That isn't
our goal here!
We're trying to eliminate
a dangerous risk!
No! I won't allow a recall.
[growls]
[NATHAN]
The executives don't understand
how serious this bug is.
We need to petition your father
to halt production of the DZs
until the patch is complete.
It's the only way to
mitigate this issue
before we have a real problem.
You know that!
[DERRIDA]
Yes, I do.
I'll talk to him in person
tomorrow, I promise.
Not now?
Hey, it's Mage's birthday today!
I can't be late to the party
because I'm waiting for
confirmation on a meeting
I might not even get to have.
[MAGE]
Coming!
[DERRIDA]
Please miss!
I've been lost in
the snow for hours!
Do you know where a sweet
girl named Mage lives?
You made it! Come in!
[MAGE, DERRIDA laugh]
[MAGE giggles]
[MAGE] Isn't it wonderful?
It all looks so delicious!
[DERRIDA] I see Mrs. Hudson
got dressed up today, too.
She sure did 'cause
it's my special day!
Be careful not to
get in her way.
You'll spill something
on your pretty dress.
[MAGE]
It'll be fine, Dad!
Yeah, let her do
what she wants, Dad.
And take a look
at what I've got...
...for you.
[MAGE gasps]
Tuberoses?!
How'd you get these?!
--Thank you!
--[DERRIDA laughs]
[DERRIDA] I knew that
they were your favorite,
and I definitely didn't
ask your father at all.
Trust me on that.
And this one is from me.
[MAGE gasps]
Can I open it now?
[NATHAN]
Mmm.
[MAGE gasps]
Pretty!
I love it! Thanks, Daddy!
[doorbell ringing]
Yuri's here! Finally!
Hello there, birthday girl!
--[camera snaps]
--Say, "cheese!"
[MAGE] I told you! Warn me
before you take my picture!
Come inside before
the snow gets in!
Hurry, hurry!
[MAGE inhales, exhales]
--[YURI] Yay!
--[DERRIDA] Happy birthday!
[NATHAN] Happy birthday!
Six, seven, eight.
No fair, you got ahead of me!
Aw! You'll catch up,
don't worry.
[YURI]
Yeah, but till then,
it'll be like you're
my big sister!
Big sister?
Yeah!
All right, Big Sis,
I've got a song for you!
Ready?
[NATHAN]
Uh-huh.
What song?
Here's a hint!
It's one of your favorites!
[click]
[piano music]
[inhales]
[YURI and SINGER]
♪ There is a colorful path ♪
♪ Which has happened ♪
♪ Vividness through
all the motions ♪
♪ colors accentuate identity ♪
♪ Time goes by ♪
[clapping]
[laughs]
[MAGE gasps]
--[NEWSCASTER softly speaks]
--[YURI] More please!
[MRS. HUDSON]
Yes, miss.
[DERRIDA]
Hm? Hold on.
We don't have
a fish pie this year?
No. Couldn't get my hands
on one, unfortunately.
[MAGE]
It's because of... the war.
[NEWSCASTER] However, things now
appear to be reversing course.
Late last night, the fighting
seemed to have
escalated once more.
According to reports at the--
Erase!
That's enough.
No sad news allowed today.
[NATHAN]
Hmm.
Just for a little longer.
Soon, everything will
go back to normal.
I hope so.
[click]
[YURI]
This is a stick-up!
Ah!
Huh?
Ha!
[YURI giggles]
I got you!
[DERRIDA]
H-Hey! Get back here!
[BOTH laughing]
--[YURI] The perfect crime!
--[DERRIDA] You little brat!
Your frowny face is
so funny, Derrida!
Ah... You'll pay for that!
--[camera snaps]
--[laughs]
[YURI]
Well, see you at school!
It'll be a whole new year!
[MAGE]
Wait, let me walk you home.
Big Sis, it's so cold,
you don't have to!
No, it's okay. Huh?
[camera snaps]
[YURI giggles]
Got you again!
[MRS. HUDSON]
Shall we be on our way?
[NATHAN]
Here you go.
This could've gotten me into
a lot of trouble
back in the day.
One more use for Automata.
A toast, to our deus ex machina.
Let's not forget that
it's Mage's birthday!
Fair enough.
To today, a special day.
[DERRIDA]
A special day.
And then, tomorrow will
be a special day, too.
Huh?
[NATHAN]
Once we finish fixing that bug,
the DZs will be complete.
Your family dream
will finally be realized.
You mean my father's dream.
I just made myself useful.
Tomorrow,
when everything's settled,
let me take you guys
out for a drink.
A drink with my old man?
Can't even imagine.
[NATHAN]
Listen, Derrida.
When this is done, will you
join me in my research?
Huh?
You mean the time jump?
[sighs] It's been a long road,
but it's nearly complete.
If I can just work out
the last few kinks--
[DERRIDA]
That old joke again?
I have to hear it tonight,
of all nights? Please.
[NATHAN]
I'm serious!
Your theory inspired me
in the first place!
[DERRIDA]
More like my pipe dream.
It was always going
to be impossible.
No, that isn't true!
Those stupid experiments
were not harmless,
they cost me a part of
my childhood memories
I can never get back.
Nathan, why are you so
obsessed with time riding?
Because it's my mission
as a scientist.
Getting labeled
a fringe scientist
won't help you in the long run.
[NATHAN]
You think it's fringe science?
[DERRIDA]
What I think is that
you should focus on
plausible subjects
and build a career before
you go there. Be realistic.
Be realistic?!
Like those executives?!
Forget my work and just focus
on how much money I can make?
[grunts]
--[NATHAN] I'm sorry.
--[DERRIDA] It's okay.
The brandy was too strong,
that's all.
I should get going anyway.
[sigh]
Oh... Mage?
Hey, show me where you're
gonna plant those tuberoses.
[chuckles]
[MAGE]
This way!
When it warms up,
I wanna plant 'em right here!
I can't wait to see how
it'll look in the spring.
[MAGE]
Hey, Derrida.
Huh?
Why won't you help my
dad with his research?
With the time ride?
Humans jumping through time
like that is just a fantasy.
It's not... possible.
[MAGE] What is the key to
traveling through time?
To memories that
can't be erased.
To special times and places.
Why do humans...
...long to return to moments
they've randomly
designated as special?
Wait, Mage?
[DERRIDA chuckles]
You're amazing.
Not really. I'm quoting
your thesis, that's all.
Dad completely believes in
the theory that you proposed.
And so do I.
[DERRIDA]
Mage, you have to understand.
I was swept away
by my fantasies.
Maybe I just wanted to
prove that romantic idea
that the missing key
to the impossible
is just wishing and hoping
and praying harder
than anyone has before you.
It's a wonderful thought!
You should prove it!
Like the first people
to ever fly,
or the ones who first explored
the depths of the ocean!
[DERRIDA] People have made
all kinds of dreams come true.
[MAGE]
Then so can you!
But after centuries of repeated
study and experiments,
one thing is clear.
We can't time travel.
But there's still a chance that
you could make the breakthrough!
Unrealized possibilities are
no different than dreams,
and I've awakened
from all of mine.
[DERRIDA] Hmph. I can't believe
I'm talking to you about this.
Uh?
Sorry. Would you give
this to your dad?
Please. Derrida. Work with him.
[DERRIDA]
Yeah. I will soon.
Really?
Sure, but now I'm gonna get
home before I freeze, okay?
[MAGE]
Do you mean it, Derrida?
[DERRIDA]
Good night, Mage.
Will you?!
If I wish hard enough?
[COMPUTER] Appointment with
Jacques Yvain confirmed.
Meeting site designated.
Finally.
[DERRIDA]
Dad?
[JACQUES]
It's been a while, Derrida.
When did you identify the issue?
[DERRIDA]
Four days ago.
[JACQUES]
Impressive.
--Swift work.
--Whatever.
Take this.
[DERRIDA] To keep the
program from being located,
I split it up around the cloud,
then Atmosed it.
Even on the off-chance
that someone finds it,
it can't be accessed
without that physical key.
I don't necessarily believe
the rumors going around
about DZs being weaponized,
but I can't let it go
if there's a chance
they could be dangerous.
Unfortunately, as their creator,
I need your help.
Do you get what I'm saying?
Son. You should avoid getting
any deeper into this.
Huh?
You... You let
Andrei pay you off!
[JACQUES]
That's not it, Derrida!
[DERRIDA]
I've been so stupid!
I don't know why
I thought you'd help me
when you've never really
acknowledged me or my work!
You named them DZs.
With a "D" for Derrida.
You gave your mechanized puppets
the same initial as your son?
I see. That's all I ever was!
[beeping]
[DERRIDA]
Nathan?
I did. It's done.
What?
Mage, no!
--[WOMAN A] Clockwise.
--[WOMAN B] Anti-clockwise.
[NATHAN]
It's nothing too serious.
She's in stable
condition for now.
I'm sorry to have
worried you, Derrida.
[DERRIDA] Well, what the
hell happened to her?
[NATHAN]
She was... doing an experiment.
All by herself, late at night.
I didn't know.
Like what?
[NATHAN sighs]
The time jump.
No way. Can you tell me
exactly what happened?
[NATHAN] I will.
At the office, tomorrow.
[phone clicks]
[crashing]
--[gun clicks]
--[JACQUES gasps]
[gunshot]
[phone rings]
[groans]
Yeah?
[NATHAN] Hurry! Get up
and get ready to leave!
What, why?
[NATHAN]
It's Andrei!
We need to get outta town. Now!
[gasps]
[panting]
[NATHAN] I got a tip off.
We're not safe.
They said that Andrei
wants both of us dead.
[gasps]
It's all been a ruse.
They've known about the bug,
and they've been
intending to exploit it.
Remember the news?
The live footage
from the war zone?
Those are militarized
DZs out there.
[gasps]
[DERRIDA]
You're kidding.
You mean they've already
been deployed into combat?
[NATHAN] That's why
he rejected the recall.
Publicizing the bug
won't help now.
And he wants us gone,
all the loose ends tied up.
[DERRIDA]
Wha... What do we do?
[NATHAN]
We get away.
As far away as possible.
[DERRIDA]
Where's Mage?
I left her over at Yuri's
house with her family.
Wha...?
She should be
safe there, for now.
I see.
Where's our access key?
I gave it to Mage last night.
What?! Why?!
[DERRIDA]
She didn't give it to you?
That means Mage is...?
[DERRIDA groans]
[DERRIDA]
Nathan! Hey!
Huh?
[NATHAN groans]
[DERRIDA]
Nathan!
[NATHAN]
Derrida... Go, run!
[ANDREI] The creator of
the Automata, Jacques Yvain,
was murdered by
his own son, Derrida,
whose good friend,
Nathan Bilstein,
acted as an accomplice.
Afterward, the two
had a falling out.
Derrida killed Nathan,
and then,
sick with guilt,
he took his own life.
What? I...
That's going to be the story
on every major news network
tomorrow morning.
You should have kept your mouth
shut and ignored that bug
--when you found it.
--You liar!
[NATHAN]
Run! Take care of Mage!
Nathan!
[gasps]
[mechanical clicking]
[ANDREI]
Fire!
[DERRIDA groans]
Nathan!
[grunts]
[ANDREI]
He can't have gone far.
Find him and kill him!
[SUBORDINATES]
Yes, sir!
[DERRIDA]
Damn... I'm fading fast.
[gasp]
Is that Mage?
No...
[gasps]
[DERRIDA grunts, yells]
[groans]
[DERRIDA]
I'm sorry, Mage. I didn't know.
I put you in danger.
[DERRIDA]
I'm so tired...
After I rest, I promise
I'll come get you.
[grunts, sighs]
[gasps]
[COMPUTER]
Cryostasis chamber activated.
Twenty seconds until
freezing is complete.
[DERRIDA]
Wait, what?
[COMPUTER] Freezing status.
Fifteen seconds remain.
No assigned duration.
Activating with
default settings.
Ten seconds remaining.
[DERRIDA]
Stop!
[COMPUTER]
Process complete in five...
...four... three...
two... one...
[DERRIDA]
Mage...
[creaking, buzzing]
[footsteps]
♪