[YURI]
That's her, but who's she with?
[DERRIDA]
That's...
Cassiel.
[DERRIDA]
Cassiel became a Destruct?
--[MAYUKA] And this. And...
--Why?
You're askin' me?
He's a researcher,
just doesn't make sense.
If you wanna know so badly,
why don't you track down the
guy and ask him yourself?
[YURI] Do we even know
where he is right now?
[VIDAUX]
Garbond, looks like.
[YURI]
That's pretty far.
[MAYUKA]
How about this?
Oh, perfect!
Tell me!
Uh, right, yeah.
Tell what?
Well, Derrida asked
her for a favor.
To keep an eye out for something
he could take notes with,
so he can do an experiment.
[MAYUKA]
And I found that!
So now you need
to keep your promise
and tell me what
your experiment is.
Yeah, you do need
to keep your promises.
"Traveling backwards in time."
If I told you it was possible,
would you believe me?
Yeah!
[DERRIDA] A "time ride" is a way
of traveling back in time
that involves sending
your consciousness
into the body
of your past self.
It's based on a hypothesis
known as the Trout Theory.
Oh, I've read about that before.
It was in that one book.
But I don't remember
what it was called.
Mayuka, just give it to him.
He can explain this
nonsense in the car.
[MAYUKA]
Okay.
[YURI]
Derrida.
Going back into the body
of your past self,
what would that accomplish?
If I could only redo
that day ten years ago,
knowing what I do now,
maybe I could save my
father and Nathan, too.
If I hadn't left that
access key with Mage,
then maybe she'd be safe instead
of being a target right now.
It was my stupid decision
that put her in danger.
[GRAHAM screaming]
[ALL gasp]
[grunts]
No use. The bypass circuit
is totally fried.
Poor Graham, are you okay?
[GRAHAM] It would be unwise
to drive under these conditions.
I recommend a diagnostic
by a specialized mechanic.
[MAYUKA grunts]
[VIDAUX]
We should find a mechanic
in the city just
a little ways off.
All the circuits in that block
are dead, so if we want help,
we'll have to bring
someone back this way.
So, do Derrida and Yuri
gotta stay here?
This time, it seems so.
Don't just stand by the road.
Find somewhere to hide.
[YURI]
How long will this take?
Probably all night.
Not ideal.
[VIDAUX sighs]
No choice.
See ya.
Anybody here?
It's definitely far
from the road.
We should be safe.
[YURI]
Mm. Huh?
Is that a photo of flowers?
Mage loved these too.
Did she?
[YURI]
You wouldn't expect it,
but Mage and I
were two of a kind.
We usually ended up loving
the exact same things.
[gasps]
Anyway! Let's split up and find
some rooms we can use, yeah?
I'll go this way.
Huh?
I've gotta tell him.
[footsteps approaching]
[BOTH]
Hm?
"My second time ride happened
in Vanfort National Museum."
Hold on.
[YURI]
I thought you were acting weird.
So you're saying
that you traveled back
into your own past
and you were able
to talk to your father?
Hard to believe.
It's true, though.
But... time rides should require
specific equipment to work.
I don't know what's going on.
About the Trout Theory.
That's the thesis
you presented, right?
How did you know that?
[YURI]
Mage told me about it.
She said that your
theory was correct.
That so?
Derrida... we need to talk.
[DERRIDA]
Hm?
[YURI]
Um... can you really do it over?
The stuff that happened
a decade ago.
[DERRIDA] The time ride
is a phenomenon
that requires vividly recalling
certain memories.
[YURI]
Hmm.
[DERRIDA] I can still remember
what happened ten years ago
like it was yesterday.
Hey, if it helps, you can look.
Huh?
At the pictures.
I don't know,
maybe they can help.
Keep your memories clear.
That's the folder of the day
you said you did
your first time ride.
This is from the day
that we infiltrated Rebuild.
Maybe one of these pictures
will show some sign
of what happened
before the time ride.
Huh? What's this?
He told us to gun it, remember?
Huh?! Oh, that's-- I mean,
I was just, uh--
Do you even have your license?
[groans] What was
I supposed to do?
We were desperate.
[grunts]
That has nothing to do
with anything, though, right?
[DERRIDA]
I'm remembering something.
Come on. Come on!
[clock slowly ticking]
[MAGE]
Pandora's box has been opened.
This is the beginning
of another journey.
For you, alone.
[gasps]
[clock ticking slowly]
[DERRIDA]
Where am I?
Nathan!
And now, he wants us gone,
all the loose ends tied up.
[DERRIDA]
I did it! I came back!
But I don't have much time.
At this point...
[NATHAN]
Look, we need to get away.
As far away as possible.
[DERRIDA]
Okay.
I know they've set up
an ambush ahead.
Where's our access key?
[DERRIDA]
I'll explain later.
Nathan, stop the car.
[grunts]
[clock ticking slowly]
[DERRIDA gasps]
Yuri, where's Nathan?
Is he okay?
Uh, you mean Mage's dad?
What about him? Nathan's dead.
I didn't change it, then.
Vivid memories
are what trigger it.
If I can just get
my memories in order,
maybe I can choose
where I leap back to.
Wait a minute,
did you just time ride?
[DERRIDA]
Mm-hmm.
But to... when?
I went back to the night
of December 22nd, 2050.
If I had to guess,
after midnight.
But that was already
too late to do something.
I need to go further back.
[engine humming]
[MAYUKA] Papa! Do you ever
want to go back to long ago?
What?
What Derrida said.
You can go back into your
old self and do things over?
Nothing in the past
can be done over.
[MAYUKA]
Huh? What'd you say?
[DERRIDA]
What? Mage, no!
[clock ticking slowly]
[NATHAN]
It's nothing too serious.
She's in stable
condition for now.
[DERRIDA]
I suspect that when I try
to make drastic changes,
history's self-correction effect
drags me back to my time.
So how far can I push?
[NATHAN] But I was planning
to cancel everything for the day
to stay with her, anyway.
[DERRIDA]
This will be fine.
[NATHAN]
Derrida, are you still there?
Yeah, I'm sorry.
When she wakes up,
tell her get well soon.
[DERRIDA]
All right, stay casual.
By the way, about Andrei.
[gasps]
[grunts]
[DERRIDA]
Tomorrow will be too late!
So, what happened to Mage?
[gasps]
Where's Nathan?
Damn it! I have no practical
way of figuring out
if I change anything!
Even if I can go back
to the exact point I want,
it's meaningless
if I can't change it.
Concentrate. Think it through.
Huh? Hey, wait, no!
Damn it.
--[thudding]
--[YURI shouts]
[YURI]
Ouch...
Huh?
What're you doing in here?
[YURI]
I was looking for these.
[DERRIDA]
Why?
Huh? I told you,
I wanted to see
if they had any
paper notebooks, remember?
Huh?
[gasps]
[DERRIDA] Did such a small
change ten years ago
really affect Yuri's
actions in the present?
If that's true...
Hey, Yuri.
Do me a favor.
Uh?
--[WOMAN A] Clockwise.
--[WOMAN B] Anti-clockwise.
Confirm three things for me.
Jacques Yvain.
He was killed ten years ago.
His death occurred on
December 21st in the year 2050.
State your answer.
Please, I need
to hear you say it.
[YURI]
I still don't understand,
but yeah, your father
died that day.
And Nathan Bilstein
did as well?
[YURI]
Yes.
[DERRIDA] And... Mage Bilstein
is currently missing?
[YURI]
Mm.
If I succeed in changing things,
this conversation will change,
which means that these
notes will be rewritten.
[YURI] Do you really think
it'll work like that?
I don't know, but it
seems worth testing.
[clock ticking slowly]
[DERRIDA]
I'm going back to investigate.
Okay, it's the morning
of Mage's birthday.
Too bad I couldn't go back
any further in time.
The access keys.
This is all pointless
if I don't complete them.
I'll avoid going any earlier
than this for now.
I'll give this to
Nathan right away.
--[grunts]
--[clock ticking slowly]
[gasps]
Anything?
[sighs]
All right.
I'll leap to every
point that I can.
Derrida.
[clock ticking slowly]
[NATHAN]
Derrida! Where are you?
[DERRIDA]
This is the ninth time.
Just catch on.
Figure it out!
[DERRIDA]
Please understand.
[laughs softly]
[grunts]
Uh! Who's there?
[DERRIDA gasps]
But why?
[gasps]
[YURI]
Hey... What's wrong?
Are you feeling all right?
You kinda seem like
you're exhausted,
like you've been
up working late.
[DERRIDA]
It's okay. I'm done for now.
Yeah? Well, let's eat then.
Hey, Yuri. Thank you.
[YURI]
Hmm?
I'd originally intended
to do these time ride
experiments all by myself.
I assumed that you'd
never believe me.
But now I'm really relieved
that I told you about it.
Uh, well,
if I'm being honest,
I don't actually get
what it is you're doing.
But whatever it is,
it's something important.
I wish I could
understand, but...
[DERRIDA chuckles]
That's more than enough, though.
Only the person actually on
the time ride can perceive it.
I have no way of proving
it's even happening.
So I would never expect you
to understand everything
that I'm trying to do with it.
You know just the fact
that you're even willing
to listen to me gives me
enormous peace of mind.
Yuri! Take our picture!
I've noticed you never take
any photos of yourself.
Well, the photographer belongs
behind the camera, so, um...
[DERRIDA] It'll be
another important "note."
[gasps]
Huh?
[knocking]
Hey, sorry, but could
I get another...
[DERRIDA]
Hm.
[gasps]
[clock ticking slowly]
[DERRIDA]
What was I just doing?
I was on my way
to the flower shop.
[DERRIDA grunts]
Whoa! When did it get this late?
[DERRIDA]
There it is again.
Another memory
I don't recognize.
This isn't my memory, is it?
[DERRIDA]
No.
[DERRIDA grunts]
This memory is...
[grunts]
[clock ticking slowly]
[DERRIDA]
What was I just doing?
I was on my way
to the flower shop.
[DERRIDA]
I knew it!
It'll be five minutes.
Please wrap the tuberoses.
They're a birthday gift.
[DERRIDA]
This is a branching timeline
created by the time ride.
Did something change?
Is that why I have
two sets of memories?
[footsteps crunching]
[DERRIDA]
I know.
Maybe if I alter
the auto-drive program
in Nathan's car,
I could put us on a route where
they won't be waiting for us.
[beeping]
[gasps]
[YURI] I can't believe
Derrida's so late to your party!
I'm sure it's only because
he's so focused on work.
Don't let him off easy!
Hey, what kind of present
do you think he got you?
[MAGE]
I'd be happy with anything.
[YURI] That's not what
I asked! You have to guess!
[MAGE] Then what if
I guess what he'll say?
[YURI]
Oh? Sure, go for it!
[MAGE]
When he gives me the present,
--[YURI] Mm-hm!
--Derrida will definitely...
[BOTH]
...say something pretentious!
[BOTH laugh]
That's all the proof
that I need.
We really are two of a kind,
aren't we, Yuri?
[YURI]
Mm.
It's freezing out here.
We should go and wait inside.
I hope Derrida doesn't
take much longer.
Huh?
[DERRIDA]
Okay, first. Nathan's car!
[clock ticking fast]
[groans]
[DERRIDA gasps]
No good.
Of course. It's common sense.
When my actions change,
the actions of the people
in the places I would have been
will end up changing, too.
Because I was late
to the birthday party,
Mage and Yuri waited for me.
[YURI] I hope Derrida
doesn't take much longer.
Good night, Yuri.
[door closes]
[YURI panting]
I'm relieved that I told you.
[YURI]
You're wrong, Derrida.
[MAGE]
Yuri, did you open this file
while I was gone,
by any chance?
I'm sorry for not asking.
I thought it was mine.
Mage?
[chuckles]
Oh, it's nothing.
It's not your fault those
people are after her.
You don't get it.
It's mine.
And yet, I...
This is just unfair, isn't it?
[gasps]
[MYSTERIOUS MAN]
Stay very still.
Make one false move and I shoot.
--[door opens]
--[gasps]
[MAYUKA panting]
What's wrong?
Big Sis is gone!
Huh?
[MAYUKA]
Papa! I found Derrida!
[DERRIDA]
What happened?
Where's Yuri?
[VIDAUX]
Look.
[gasps]
Yuri.