[clattering, sizzling]
[DERRIDA]
Wait! It's me! It's Derrida!
Yeah, right.
That can't be true.
No, Derrida is...
Listen to me. Where's Mage?
Is she somewhere safe?
Just tell me, please!
I'm sorry.
[YURI]
Mage is dead.
That just can't be.
[breeze blowing]
Mage is dead?
♪
Come with me.
Hmm?
[grunting]
[DERRIDA]
I thought this was a park.
[YURI]
It was, but that was years ago.
Take a look.
♪
But that's... impossible.
[DERRIDA]
Mage...
I'm sorry, but it's true.
She's buried right here.
[DERRIDA]
No way.
Tell me. What...
What killed her?
How could this have
happened to her?
[YURI]
What do you think?
It was the war, of course.
And it wasn't just her.
Do you know how many
casualties there've been?
[DERRIDA]
The war.
I've been gone for 10 years,
and this is what I wake up to?
[YURI]
Seriously, who are you?
[DERRIDA]
Hmm?
[gasp]
I'm Derrida! Derrida Yvain!
I'm a friend of Mage's father,
Nathan, don't you remember?
You have to remember me!
You were Mage's friend,
you love cameras and--
You're a liar! Derrida's dead!
That man killed Nathan Bilstein,
-And then he killed himsel--
-No, you're wrong!
That's not true, I was framed!
By that snake,
Andrei, at Rebuild.
♪
[wind blowing]
[jewels clinking]
[DONNA] Souls of the dead
deserve respect.
Didn't anyone ever teach you
that when you visit a grave,
you're supposed
to bring flowers?
[YURI]
Huh?
Who are...?
-[breeze]
-[grunt]
♪
[energy humming]
[chuckle]
[blast]
[VIDAUX]
Derrida! Back away from her!
[gunfire]
[cloak whipping]
[slice]
-Get going!
-[slice]
Hurry to Graham, now!
[yelp]
Not so fast.
[panting]
[grunting]
-[grunt]
-[gasp]
[VIDAUX grunts]
How dare you.
I can't have you
hurting my client.
-[grunting]
-[blade clinking]
[groaning]
[DONNA]
I only have one target,
but if you get in my way...
-[panting]
-[DERRIDA] Come on, this way!
-Get in!
-[grunt]
I don't know who you
people are, but I'm not--
Hey, Graham! Please save Vidaux!
[GRAHAM] Negative. I have been
ordered to protect Mayuka.
Papa!
I told you to stay inside!
Oh no! You're bleeding!
[VIDAUX]
It's okay, sweetheart.
Who the hell did you piss off
to get her on your tail?
-What?
-That's Donna, the White Death.
An assassin who'll
chase her prey
all the way to
the depths of Hell.
-Way past being just a Destruct.
-[pressing buttons]
She's the most terrifying
killer out there.
And she's coming after me?
[VIDAUX]
And I wanna know why!
[gasp]
People don't hire
someone like her
unless it's pretty damn serious.
This is gonna cost you extra!
-[engine roaring]
-[wind blowing]
[GRAHAM]
Target locked from behind.
[cocks gun]
Let's shake her off!
[blast]
-[tires screech]
-[explosion]
[screeching]
♪
-[phone ringing]
-Huh?
Excuse me for just a moment.
[chuckling]
[cough]
It's me. What is it?
[DONNA]
I'm changing the plan.
Huh? What are you going to do?
I don't want you drawing atten--
[DONNA] The state of battle
is in constant flux.
-[hangs up]
-Hold on, wait a second!
Did you hang up? Hello?!
[clicking]
[uncocks gun]
[YURI] Hey, where do you
think you're going?
I'm not a part of this,
you hear me?
[VIDAUX] Then you can
go ahead and jump out.
Um... Do you think you could
maybe pull over first?
I won't stop until I'm sure
we're in a safe place.
That's one of my
regulations, kid.
[sigh]
But, we're not even
being followed anymore.
[VIDAUX] You really believe
that she'll give up that easily?
[sigh]
This is all your fault.
You're the reason
I'm wrapped up in this.
It isn't exactly
pleasant for me, either.
It's like some kind
of twisted nightmare.
Mage's dead, and I'm being
hunted down by a killer?
What the hell is wrong
with this godforsaken place?!
[MAYUKA]
He told this weird story.
about how he's been
asleep for 10 years!
For 10 years?
-[beeping]
-[GRAHAM] Target locked!
-Behind and above!
-[gasp]
-[jets whining]
-I knew she'd be back!
He musta been someone really
important back then, huh?
Yeah, well, he doesn't look all
that special, if you ask me.
♪
[VIDAUX] Hey, how much
more can I put on your tab?
Protecting you from
her won't come cheap.
Whatever, I don't care!
Charge as much as you want!
Hmm...
Sounds like something a guy
with no money would say.
Alright everyone, hold tight!
-[restraints clicking]
-Huh? What--
[roaring]
[gunfire]
-[tires screeching]
-[screaming]
[VIDAUX] Mouth shut!
You'll bite your tongue off!
Hey Graham,
any base camps nearby?
[GRAHAM]
Camp Exon is approximately
-four kilometers ahead.
-[beeping]
Got it.
-[gunfire]
-[tires screeching]
[jets whining]
You won't escape.
[beeping]
-[gunfire]
-[tires screeching]
[engine roaring]
[groaning]
[gunfire]
[explosions]
[tires screeching]
[GRAHAM]
800 meters to base camp.
It's about to get bumpy.
♪
We're almost there.
[tires screeching]
-[thud]
-[roaring]
[smash]
Do you really think
it'll be that easy?
[machinery whirring]
[launching]
[explosions]
[YURI]
The way out!
[rocks tumbling]
[jets whining]
[ANDREI gasping]
[LILY]
Spill imminent.
Warning. Milk tea will spill.
-[splash]
-Milk tea has spilled.
[ANDREI]
That woman!
What the hell does
she think she's doing?
-Is she out of her mind?!
-[splat]
Oh... my shortcake!
[car whirring, clattering]
[click, buzz]
[VIDAUX]
Okay, everyone out.
[YURI sighs]
Finally.
[MAYUKA]
Whoa...
[YURI sighs]
Where are we?
[VIDAUX]
A supply base for emergencies.
I have a few others
hidden here and there.
♪
-[click]
-Can I take pictures in here?
[VIDAUX]
Knock yourself out.
Hey, will you take my picture?
[sigh]
Sure.
-Mmm!
-[shutter clicks]
[sigh]
Damn it. She really got us good.
[shutter click]
You ambushed me
like that before.
You haven't changed.
When did I do that?
Mage's birthday party.
When she turned 8 years old.
But, that was so many
years ago. Are you sure?
To me, it's like it
was just yesterday.
[VIDAUX] Hey, Derrida.
Come here for a minute.
Sure.
-[sigh]
-[clicking]
[YURI]
10 years ago.
At Mage's birthday party?
♪
Oh, come on.
There's just no way.
[sigh]
[camera clicks]
Are you really him?
You're Derrida?
-[wrench cranking]
-Is there a way
-for us to get out?
-[VIDAUX] Yeah, a back entrance.
[sigh]
Hand me that ratchet, will you?
So? [clears throat]
What happens now?
What do you mean?
[VIDAUX] I don't mind
being your bodyguard,
if you can pay me eventually.
But, if that girl's
gonna keep following you,
I'm gonna need to charge extra.
Number four wrench.
[rummages]
Listen, I'll pay you.
Please just take
Yuri home for me.
Are you really that valuable,
do you think?
[cranking]
Probably.
[VIDAUX]
And what if you're not?
-Number two.
-[rummages]
Then, I guess...
I'll be your servant for life.
Not that one! I said number two!
Right.
Sorry.
[wrench cranking]
[WOMAN, overlapping]
Clockwise. Anti-clockwise.
[YURI]
There's a city up ahead.
You can stock up on
food at the market.
[VIDAUX]
Sounds good.
[car approaching]
[YURI]
Alright.
-[MAYUKA gasps]
-Is this close enough?
Yeah, this'll work great!
What a big city!
[DERRIDA] It looks like the war
-has reached here too.
-[VIDAUX] Which way
-is the market?
-Follow me, I'll show you.
[crowd chatter]
♪
[VIDAUX]
Hmm...
-[smack]
-[MAYUKA groans]
[WOMAN]
Oh, Yuri!
It's been so long!
Dear, come here, it's Yuri!
Oh! How 'bout that, doing well?
Did you happen to find
what you were looking for?
Huh?
Oh, uh, no, not yet!
[WOMAN] That's too bad.
I hope you find it soon!
Yeah! Thank you!
Hey. What's with this place?
Uh...
[sigh]
[YURI] It was built
after the war started.
Most of the residents
made their way here
as refugees from all over,
after being driven
from their homes.
I see.
-[VIDAUX] You two.
-[BOTH] Hmm?
What are you staring at?
Let's get going,
we're done here.
[DERRIDA]
Got it.
[sigh]
♪
-[MAYUKA] What a haul!
-[VIDAUX sighs]
Glad they had a lot of
good stuff for sale.
Yuri.
I'm sorry I dragged
you into this.
Guess it's time
for goodbyes.
Thanks.
[sigh]
-No, wait!
-Huh?
[birds chirping]
[footsteps]
You and Mage.
This is where both of you lived?
Yeah.
[twists knob, door creaks]
[flips switch, lights buzz]
-Mrs. Hudson?
-Um...
What's she doing here?
[YURI] She's been
with us the whole time.
Taking care of me and Mage.
How's her battery?
Well, I put her in
sleep mode a while ago.
She was a precious friend
to us when we were little,
and I suppose
she still is, to me.
I see. You've had her.
-Um...
-Huh?
Here.
Pictures.
Is that Mage?
-I have some here, too!
-Oh.
How do you use that again?
You go like this, here. See?
♪
Oh yeah, and then
after this happened,
Nathan told me he left
Mage at your house.
Yeah. At first, the two of
us stayed with my family.
But then, the war got worse,
and they decided that it
would be best to go abroad.
However, Mage and I didn't
want to leave the country.
We convinced my parents
to let us stay,
and we lived here.
Every so often,
people from Rebuild,
or the police,
would come by to see us.
[gasp]
They kept asking,
"Has Derrida been here?".
Pretty weird, isn't it?
If you believed the news,
that was a dead man.
[sigh]
But Mage was convinced
the media was wrong.
That Derrida was still alive.
That he'd come here
for us one day.
[sigh]
[DERRIDA] Mage believed in me,
even after what happened?
But, I was too late!
[sob]
I didn't make it in time.
Uh...
[sigh]
Well I, uh...
I haven't been...
-truthful.
-Huh?
She's actually...
-alive.
-[gasp]
♪
Hmm?
[VIDAUX]
What the...
What are you talking about?
You said...
you said she had died!
She had a grave!
That's...
-a fake that I made.
-Huh?
I knew that someone
was after Mage,
and I had to do
something to protect her.
So, I pretended
that she was dead,
and I put up
the grave as a decoy.
Then where is she right now?
That, I don't know.
Without telling me,
she ran off somewhere last fall.
I've been searching
for her, but...
[sigh]
All of this is my fault.
I gave her that thing,
and because of that,
she's in danger now.
[growl]
We need to go
and track her down!
Derrida...
I believe you,
-and your story.
-Huh?
When you were crying earlier,
it didn't look like
crocodile tears.
You were genuinely concerned!
Yuri, I...
And I also believe
you when you say
that you came here
from 10 years ago.
Crazy as it is.
Oh Yuri, thank you!
If Mage is still alive,
-I know we can find her!
-[birds cawing]
I'll go get Vidaux.
[footsteps]
[wind blowing]
-[crackling]
-[gasp]
Is this fog?
[gasp]
♪
-[clock ticking slower]
-[energy humming]
It's you again.
[inaudible]
Ange, right?
What are you trying to tell me?
[clock ticking faster]
[energy humming]
Wait, was she...
pointing at Yuri?
[growl]
-[click]
-[air rushing]
[explosion]
Yuri, no! I'm coming!
[glass shattering]
[YURI coughing, choking]
[gasping, panting]
Just hang on!
[panting]
[groaning]
[screaming]
[grunting]
[debris falling]
[whimpering]
Yuri! You okay?
[DERRIDA]
You're safe now. Can you stand?
[YURI]
Yeah.
[gasp]
I need to save her!
-Yuri, wait!
-Mrs. Hudson!
And my pictures of Mage!
-No!
-Let me go!
You can't!
-If you go in, you'll...
-[crying]
[engine revving, tires screech]
[VIDAUX]
Get in.
[door closes, engine roars]
[dust flying]
Damn, I can't believe
they'd blow up
the whole building
just to get to you.
Do you think it was that woman
from the gravesite again?
[VIDAUX]
No, probably someone else.
I saw some shady
guys lurking around
-just before the explosion.
-[DERRIDA sighs]
I've really got my hands
full with the two of you.
I'm sorry. I'm sorry.
[crying]
Mage.
[breeze blowing]
-[ringing]
-[ANDREI] It's me.
This wasn't part of
the plan we agreed on.
Did you order this?
[laughing]
Whatever do you mean?
-Stop interfering, you fool.
-[gasp]
If you're going to insist on
sending others after my target,
be prepared for
collateral damage.
-[hangs up]
-[gasp]
Hey! Hello?!
She hung up again!
[grunt] Hang up on me,
I'll hang you up!
How dare you do this to me,
I deserve better!
♪
[VIDAUX]
We've been through a lot today.
I think we've earned some rest.
Yeah, I'm tired!
[opens trunk]
Yuri...
I'm sorry.
If only we hadn't gone
to your house, then...
Tomorrow, I'll talk to Vidaux,
and have him take you to
go find your parents, okay?
I'll look for Mage myself.
And if I find her,
I promise that
I'll let you know.
Count on it.
-No, I won't.
-Huh?
[grunt]
'Cause I'm going, too,
-to help search for Mage!
-Huh?
Besides,
not like I have
anywhere to go,
thanks to you mixing
me up in all this!
But you know we could get
attacked again at any time!
Well, I don't care!
I'll face any danger head-on
if it means that I get
to see Mage again!
And that's final.
I've made up my mind!
I'll be joining the team!
-Huh?
-Are you really, Yuri?
And who exactly's
paying your way?
-Oh, you know.
-Uh...
I get it!
Really, now.
[MAYUKA] Yay!
I get to stay with Big Sis!
[VIDAUX] I'll expect full
compensation for this.
-Keep that in mind.
-[grunt]
Sure! You can just
put it all on my tab!
[giggle]