♪
[MAYUKA]
I’m bored!
[yawn]
It’s been nothing but
desert outside for hours.
Are we really heading
the right way?
Garbond’s run-down, and out
in the middle of nowhere.
Perfect hiding place for
men with guilty consciences.
[MAN ON RADIO]
Status report?
Another voice?
Hey, I’ve been meaning to ask
about those transmissions.
What are they?
[VIDAUX]
I’m tapping into communications
from local police scanners.
We’re all on the lam, after all.
[DERRIDA]
Right.
[VIDAUX] Don’t worry.
Haven’t heard anything bad yet.
-[MAYUKA] Hey, look!
-[BOTH] Huh?
[MAYUKA] It says 50 kilometers
to the next city!
[VIDAUX] Guess we’ll make
it before sundown, at least.
[engine roar]
Do you think we’ll
find Mage there?
[DERRIDA]
That security camera footage
was from quite a while back.
She might not be in
the city anymore.
[YURI]
But maybe,
we’ll find some kind of clue,
-or...
-[explosions]
-What the?!
-What was that?!
That’s not good!
-[DERRIDA] Ah!
-[rocks tumbling]
-[grunt]
-[engine roar]
[rocks crashing]
[explosion]
That seemed like a trap.
Those government guys again?
-[DERRIDA] Or Donna?
-[VIDAUX] Buckle up!
[DISTORTED VOICE]
Exit the highway now.
If you rush forward
trying to avoid this,
you’ll get caught
in the real trap.
Who are you?
-[VOICE] You’ve been advised.
-[BOTH gasp]
[DERRIDA]
What just happened?
[GRAHAM] Our radio tap
system was intercepted
by an outside source.
Unable to pinpoint
the signal’s origin.
We can’t change routes!
If we leave the highway,
it’ll take longer.
But what if it
really is dangerous
to keep on going this way?
-[VIDAUX sighs]
-[engine roar]
[grunt]
[tires screech]
[DONNA]
What?
Was I detected?
No.
[ANDREI on phone]
Donna?
Is it true you haven’t
finished Derrida off yet?
Say something, I want answers!
You’re a clever little rat.
I see that you decided
to listen in on me.
[gasp]
I wasn’t eavesdropping at all!
[DONNA]
A pitiful rat,
who foolishly trampled
upon Death’s shadow.
[ANDREI]
Wait, Death?
I...
I haven’t trampled on anything!
[DONNA]
That was a mistake.
You won’t live to see
the light of another day.
Your time in this world will
be cut short by Death’s scythe.
[gasp]
Wait, Donna please, spare me,
-I’m begging--!
-[hangs up]
[engine roars]
[wind blowing]
[MAYUKA] Ah!
There are real beds here, right?
-[YURI] And showers, too?!
[DERRIDA] Is this wise?
Staying at a hotel seems
like asking to be attacked.
[VIDAUX]
Not if it’s Donna.
She’ll only strike in places
without many people around.
She doesn’t seem the type to
worry about casualties, though.
[VIDAUX]
She prefers not to reveal her MO
to anyone but her targets.
The heavy weapons’ll
slow you down,
but when she kills,
she makes it personal.
So even if she mixes
in with a crowd,
she won’t try to blow
us up with a bomb
or anything
we can’t see coming.
A veteran assassin like Donna
would never alter her style.
I’ll meet up with you all later.
You’re not coming upstairs,
Papa?
I’m gonna go look around.
You stay here.
-I want to come with you.
-No.
I need you to stick with
Mayuka and Yuri for me.
Just in case, okay?
Mm-hmm.
♪
[BARTENDER]
What’ll it be?
Just milk.
[laughter]
[BARTENDER]
Sorry, pal,
but we’ve only
got the hard stuff here.
Not bad at all!
Let’s get a round for
the whole house, on me!
[cheering]
Actually,
I’m looking for someone.
[YURI] I’m getting
the hot water started!
[MAYUKA, YURI giggle]
[DISTORTED VOICE]
Exit the highway now.
You’ve been advised.
[DERRIDA]
“Advised”, huh?
[yawn]
[groan]
[YURI giggles]
♪
[sigh]
-[YURI] Aren’t you gonna sleep?
-Probably in a bit.
Don’t wait up for me, okay?
You look like something’s
on your mind. What’s up?
When do I ever not have
something on my mind?
That voice. The one we heard
on the comm this afternoon.
I feel like I’ve heard
it somewhere before.
Really? Recently?
Think so.
It wasn’t that long ago.
Though, uh...
I guess it was about
10 years ago for you.
How did you recognize it
through the distortion?
Didn’t have to.
It's the distorted voice
that’s familiar.
[VIDAUX]
Both of you are still up?
You should be taking
this chance to rest.
You find out
anything out there?
[VIDAUX]
Nothing about Mage.
However, I did learn that
there’s a Destruct in town
who sounds like
he could be Cassiel.
What? You’re kidding me!
Where is he?
That info, I couldn’t get.
He’s a very cautious guy,
it seems.
[sigh]
One more bit of bad news.
Rumor has it there’s someone
else looking for Cassiel.
A woman with a scar on her face.
Sounds like Donna!
But why is she here?
Maybe she traced him
based on the information
in the file we stole
from Rebuild.
Oh, great.
-We need to find him first!
-[radio static]
[DISTORTED VOICE]
Don’t be hasty.
[gasp]
Impossible!
My ID is void.
-It can’t get calls!
-Destroy that thing, now!
[DISTORTED VOICE]
Oh?
But you listened to my
advice on the highway,
and that turned
out in your favor.
Hang on a second.
I get it now.
It’s you, isn’t it, Cassiel?
I’m right, aren’t I?
Huh?
You saying that’s him? You sure?
I remember.
Just before I could
finish up the patch file,
I got a call that
warned me to review
the quality control
process for the DZs.
He scrambled his voice
the same way.
Isn’t that correct, Cassiel?
[CASSIEL] You remember one
phone call from 10 years ago?
It wasn’t actually
10 years ago for me.
[CASSIEL]
Cryostasis, then.
It’s just as
Mage Bilstein said.
You spoke with her?!
[CASSIEL] I knew you’d
come here eventually.
I want to talk to you.
Yeah, me too!
[gasp]
We’d all like to meet you.
What’s your location?
[CASSIEL]
No. You’re under observation
of that assassin, Donna.
How do you know?
And we just heard a rumor that
she’s going after you, too, now.
That’s what she’s up to.
She intentionally let
that information slip
to the bartender
to get all of us to panic.
[CASSIEL] Her plan is to
have you search for me,
and then finish us
all off together.
I don’t think she appreciated
me tapping her communications.
What’re you planning to do?
I’ll leak information
on my whereabouts
to draw the attention
away from you.
At dawn, leave the hotel
and drive west on the highway.
I’ll find you from there.
Careful not to
underestimate Donna.
[CASSIEL]
I won’t.
Plus, I have a bit of
an ace-in-the-hole myself.
-See you at dawn.
-[hangs up]
[YURI sighs]
♪
[sigh]
[VIDAUX]
It’s almost time.
Let them sleep as
long as possible.
Not often they get real beds.
-[VIDAUX] Derrida...
-Hmm?
Before, you talked
about turning back time
in order to do the past over.
It’s alright if you
don’t believe me.
I just wanna know,
if the past got changed,
where would we be right now?
For instance,
if the two of us hadn’t met,
and I didn’t pull you
out of that battlefield...
Assuming I got lucky
and survived, then...
I guess I’d probably
be here, but alone.
And, the memory
of you saving me,
would be sequestered off to
an inaccessible part of my mind.
Like a dream you
forget upon waking.
[VIDAUX]
A dream...
But I’ve learned that I can’t
change the past
that significantly.
The moment that I try,
I’m kicked back to the present.
The most I can do
is say a few words
to someone, that’s all.
I see.
Why’d you wanna know?
[VIDAUX]
I’m gonna go check on Graham.
We’re moving out,
wake them up for me.
[door opens, closes]
-[breeze blowing]
-[engine humming]
[YURI]
It’s quiet.
[DERRIDA]
So far, everything’s gone
according to Cassiel’s plan.
I wouldn’t be so sure.
-[DERRIDA] Donna!
-[gun clicking]
♪
[VIDAUX]
She outmaneuvered us.
She wants to try
and chase us down
in order to lure Cassiel out.
But even so, no one could
possibly hit us at this dista--
-[blast]
-[smash]
[BOTH gasp]
[GRAHAM] Damage to
shock-absorption system.
Immediate stop requested.
Yeah, like hell we’re stopping!
[engine roar]
[chuckle]
We’ve gotta move!
She’s gaining on us!
-[blast]
-[MAYUKA] Ah!
Get down!
[tires screech]
[VIDAUX growls]
Get outta my way,
stupid hunk of junk!
[CASSIEL] Is that any way
to talk to your savior?
Cassiel!
[ramp whirring, thud]
[engine roaring]
[DONNA laughing]
Well, it would seem that
I’ve finally smoked
the rat out from its hole!
Get away from her, Cassiel!
[DONNA]
Dawn.
That’s the moment Death’s
scythe will find your neck.
Incorrect.
Your artificial arm
is a prototype,
a late-generation refurbish.
I know because I’m one of
the people who developed it.
[blast]
[grunt]
[scream]
[grunting]
[clattering]
[CASSIEL]
This is an anti-pulse generator.
It simulates a command from the
brain stem to the prosthetic,
locking it up involuntarily.
That’s impressive.
Did you design it?
Very ironic.
This device is evidence
of my original sin,
and yet it ended up
saving your life
-10 years after its creation.
-Huh?
Derrida Yvain.
I can’t begin to tell
you how happy I am
that you’re still among us.
But now,
I must apologize.
-[energy humming]
-[VIDAUX] I see.
So that’s why
they can’t find you.
Rebuild certainly isn’t happy
that I’m still pottering
around unchecked.
I couldn’t go as
far as cryostasis,
but I needed to hide
myself from them somehow.
So, I was right.
You were the one behind
that anonymous call
I got 10 years ago.
Andrei needed an engineer’s
help for his scheme to work,
so I altered the QC process,
ensuring that the bug in the DZs
wouldn’t come to light in time
for anything to
be done about it.
I eventually decided to try
and warn you and Nathan,
but by then it was too late.
I’m sorry, Cassiel.
If only I had
understood your warning.
[CASSIEL]
No.
It’s my fault for
being so vague,
just to save my own hide.
If I had known then
that you’d found the bug
and completed a patch file,
maybe I would've been
less of a coward.
Because that’s something not
even Andrei could have foreseen.
It’s impressive.
[DERRIDA] I could say
the same about that device
you used to stop Donna earlier.
[device clinks]
Nah, this is just
something I rigged up.
Keeping the DZ bug hidden
was such a priority
that I skipped the QA
on this unit entirely.
And so, the defects in
the DMZ 2580 slipped right by.
And that’s what you meant
by your “original sin.”
So after hiding away in
this box for so long,
why’d you decide
to help us out now?
Atonement, perhaps.
I knew the secret,
but couldn’t make it public.
Before long, just as I feared,
war broke out.
I lost my wife and my children.
I was happy when Mage
showed up and asked for my help.
If there was
anything I could do,
I knew I wanted to assist her.
What did she end
up asking of you?
She requested various things
that would help her hold her own
and survive out
there by herself.
And one more thing,
that I couldn’t
really understand...
She wanted furniture
and equipment
that were identical to
what she had in her home
when she was living
with her father.
What would she
need all that for?
She never did give me a reason.
And after that, she just said
she was going to a quiet place.
Wonder what that means.
♪
Why can’t I kill him?
Is God protecting that man
from death at my hands?
Angelica.
You poor child.
There’s no need to worry.
I have kept the damage
to a minimum.
You can continue to act.
Yes, and I too can
continue to act.
I cannot leave
Derrida Yvain alive.
Nor the one foolishly
trying to assist him.
Using a device like that.
Does the man think
he’s God or something?
Oh, yes, Angelica.
He cannot be forgiven.
[wind blowing]
This cannot be forgiven.
♪
-Look, the water is so blue!
-[giggle] So I see!
[footsteps]
[panting]
[heavy breathing]
[CASSIEL]
My hideout is over this way.
When Mage first met me, she had
just found you in cryostasis,
and was desperately
researching any possible method
she could use to unfreeze you.
Saving you was the only
mission on her mind back then.
Hold on a sec.
Are you saying that the person
who got me out of
stasis was Mage?
Does the term “Trout Theory”
ring any bells for you?
No way.
[CASSIEL]
Mage mentioned it many times.
She said it was an important
theory, about memory and time.
[wind blowing]
-[groan]
-Derrida?
The Trout Theory was
my old research thesis
from when I was just a student.
But experimentation
was too dangerous,
so I never substantiated it.
Oh, I see.
[DERRIDA]
It was a long time ago.
Now that Nathan’s dead,
there’s no one left
to carry it on.
-Except Mage.
-[DERRIDA] Huh?
That’s why she was looking
for a quiet place.
She was going to pick up
where you and Nathan left off.
She was?
Then Mage is in serious danger!
-[groaning]
-[gasp]
[wind howling]
Huh? This is the time ride fog.
[grunt, thud]
-Derrida!
-[gasp]
-[air rushing]
-[smash]
-[grunt]
-Run for it!
-[slice]
-[gasp]
-[DERRIDA] Vidaux!
-[wind howling]
[VIDAUX groans]
Derrida Yvain,
it’s time to atone for your sin.
What’re you...
You are the son
of Jacques Yvain.
The man who built the DZs.
The sinner who made
us what we are.
The pretender who thinks
of himself as the Creator.
I don’t--
[groan]
[wind howling]
♪
[DERRIDA]
What’s going on?
Creator? Sinner?
Vidaux!
We need to get him treatment!
[ANGE]
Time ride, irregular.
Jumping to critical point,
-furthest from singularity.
-[clock ticking slower]
[typing]
Come on. Almost there.
I need to finish up this
patch file before tomorrow.
[DERRIDA]
This is... my lab.
The day before Mage’s birthday.
What happened that day?
-[typing]
-[ringing]
An inter-office call?
I didn’t know anyone but me
stayed here this late.
-[ringing continues]
-[DERRIDA] Of course!
This must be the message
from Cassiel!
Damn. My consciousness is weaker
than in previous time rides.
I can’t affect
anything like this!
Yes, hello?
[CASSIEL, distorted]
Derrida Yvain,
investigate DMZ 2580.
What are you talking about?
And who is this?
[CASSIEL] The testing process
has been secretly canceled.
If you look into it, you’ll
discover the major cover-up
that has taken place.
[DERRIDA]
In this moment,
I already knew about the bug.
But Cassiel didn’t know that.
This is the office of
a senior developer.
If you wanna request a debug,
tell a test engineer about it.
-[CASSIEL] You’ve been advised.
-Wait.
[DERRIDA]
Yes, good!
There has to be some way.
A way to change the future!
[DERRIDA]
Is this a whistleblower call?
-[CASSIEL] Well...
-I don’t know who you are,
so you must realize...
[DERRIDA]
Should I try to convince Cassiel
to tell me the situation?
No...
Considering my past self,
I’d just end up getting angry
and ruining Dad’s plan.
There must be another...
Do you have any
evidence of this?
[CASSIEL]
You want proof?
I don’t have time for
a wild goose chase
stemming from
baseless information.
[groan]
[DERRIDA]
Am I reaching my limit?
Wait! Just a little more time!
It’s no use! [groaning]
I can’t hold on,
and I haven’t changed
a damn thing again!
[grunt]
-[DONNA] What’s wrong?
-Huh?
Derrida Yvain.
Is fear going to stop your heart
before I can have the pleasure?
I won’t let you be a martyr.
Your punishment will be
delivered by Death itself!
[DERRIDA gasps]
-[gasps]
-[DERRIDA grunts]
-[gasp]
-[blast]
-[sizzling]
-[groaning] Impossible!
-[clatter]
-[gasp]
[panting]
♪
[groaning]
[CASSIEL]
Jump!
[air rushing]
[clock ticking slower]
[CASSIEL] Invert the pulse
of control test unit 25,
and use it on DMZ 2580.
We have those units here,
so I suppose it wouldn’t hurt.
I’ll check it later.
I need to complete
my current project first.
[air rushing]
[splash]
[panting]
The control test unit.
But why?
Let’s just say I owe
it all to your advice.
Huh?
It’s hard to explain,
but I’ll do my best.
[sigh] If this is gonna be
a long talk, can we save it?
[engine humming]
[DERRIDA]
Thank you again, Cassiel.
[CASSIEL]
I meant to save you,
but you saved me instead.
If that’s how you feel,
could I ask you a favor?
It’s a dangerous request,
though.
If you want me to draw away
Donna and the bounty hunters,
then I’ll gladly
take it on for you.
I won’t need too long.
Just three days.
[CASSIEL] That wound will take
at least a month to heal.
[VIDAUX]
It’ll heal while I fight.
We don’t have much time
before the scorched Earth blast.
[CASSIEL sighs]
I’ve spread word you’re
in a trailer heading east.
That false lead should
throw them off the scent,
at least for the time being.
I’ll try to hold
out for two weeks.
You do that, and we’re even.
[DERRIDA]
Wait a minute.
Since when were
there bounty hunters?
And what exactly is
the scorched Earth blast?
[gasp]
[blasts]
♪
But those are missiles.
[VIDAUX]
More bombing tests.
You serious?
They might fire off
the big one any day now,
and then we’ll all be really--
[groan]
-[MAYUKA whines]
-Don’t force yourself to talk!
-You’ll reopen your wound.
-Papa! No, Papa!
Hey, no need to worry
about your old man.
Did that time ride really
cause such a massive change?
I had no idea it
could be so powerful.
There’s no other choice now,
I need to redo that
moment one more time!
-[clock ticking slower]
-[wind howling]
[ANGE]
That is impossible.
The time ride is
not all-powerful.
Changes to any given past
event can only be made once.
What do you mean?
[ANGE]
Two conflicting memories
exist together within
your consciousness.
You cannot travel
to that time again.
You’re kidding me!
[ANGE] Traveling back
to a certain moment,
and the alteration
of that moment,
is allowed only once.
[DERRIDA]
How many times
have I time ridden without
knowing that key detail?
How many moments
have I rendered
permanently unchangeable?