[DERRIDA] Please miss! I've
been lost in the snow for hours!
Do you know where
a sweet girl named Mage lives?
You made it! Come in!
[BOTH laughing]
♪
[DERRIDA] My memories have
definitely been changed.
You mean her birthday
party 10 years ago?
But, you were late that day.
Huh?
[YURI] I mean, you got there
after I did, at least.
[click]
Hmm...
[MAGE]
Coming!
[doors creak]
You're late, Derrida!
-[thud]
-[grunt]
[YURI laughing]
[DERRIDA]
Uh, happy birthday, Mage!
Did I... change things...
with a time ride?
Did I experience
a different past?
[DERRIDA]
Uh, happy birthday, Mage!
[laughing]
It's not that funny,
stop laughing!
Does that mean the time ride
was a success after all?
[grunt]
-[YURI] Derrida!
-Hmm?
We've got one!
It's a clue about Mage!
[typing]
[YURI]
Here, take a look.
Vanfort Museum of Modern Life?
-What'd she be doing there?
-[YURI sighs]
[YURI] I don't know,
but maybe we can find a hint?
That museum's not
that far from here.
[engine roaring]
[MAYUKA]
It's supposed to be a really,
really big museum right?
What kind of stuff do they have?
[YURI] Um...
I've actually never been there.
Derrida, I need to take care
of some business of my
own while we're there.
Sure, like what?
There's a request
that I was given.
Just something
I was asked to retrieve,
if I was ever in Vanfort.
It shouldn't really
take too much time.
Understood.
You do whatever
you gotta do then.
[engine roaring, dust flying]
[chuckle]
Found you.
♪
[buzzing]
[DERRIDA]
It's totally deserted.
[YURI] There was a major battle
here about a year ago, I think.
[gasp]
Do I hafta stay here again?
We don't know what
we might run into.
[YURI] You can't always
just leave her here.
I don't bring her
with me on jobs.
[YURI]
Okay.
I'll show you some
pictures later, Mayuka.
Yay! You're the best, Big Sis!
And you're not, Papa.
[pout]
-[VIDAUX grumbles]
-She just misses you.
Let's go so we can hurry back.
[VIDAUX]
Fine.
[doors creak]
What was this building used
for back in the day anyway?
♪
[DERRIDA]
It was a police station.
-[debris crumbling]
-[YURI, DERRIDA gasp]
-[DERRIDA] An Automata?
-[humming]
[AUTOMATA]
Intruders detected.
-[click]
-Do not attempt to resist.
Put your hands up.
-[DERRIDA] Is it broken?
-[VIDAUX] What's wrong?
Hmm...
There's no way.
[AUTOMATA]
Initiating facial recognition.
Confirmed. Inspector Volker.
-[buzzing]
-[clicking]
Switching to support mode.
[winding down]
-Uh...
-[gasp]
[YURI]
It shut down.
Inspector, huh?
Not for a long time now.
[VIDAUX] So, some of them
are still operational.
[YURI] Didn't take
you for a policeman.
There you are.
[DERRIDA] This is one of
the later-generation
police models
put out by Rebuild.
They were pretty
compact by then.
Were you the one
that developed them?
Only the base system.
I wasn't directly involved.
-[YURI sighs]
-[footsteps]
[VIDAUX]
Okay, I'm back.
Let's head for the museum.
[wind blowing]
-[YURI giggling]
-[snapping pictures]
I can't wait for
Mayuka to see these!
[DERRIDA]
Strange. I feel like...
I've been here before.
Huh?
[breeze blowing]
Wow! It's huge!
♪
[wind howling]
[gasping]
[clock ticking slowly]
♪
[gasp]
[laughing]
[rumbling]
[doors slide]
[laugh]
[clock ticking slowly]
I'm with Dad?
Did... I ever go out
with him like this?
[wind blowing]
[groan]
What's going on here?
[footsteps]
[YURI]
Look at that. A celestial globe?
[gasp]
[YURI]
I know this!
[beeping, humming]
[pulse]
[sparkling]
♪
Oh, wow! It's gorgeous!
How pretty!
[YOUNG DERRIDA]
So cool!
[gasp]
[YOUNG DERRIDA]
Don't you think so, Dad?
[JACQUES]
Try looking at it from the side.
Huh?
[YOUNG DERRIDA gasps, laughs]
It looks totally different!
From the side, you can see
which ones are closer
and which are further away!
Dad, listen!
The starlight in the sky
is from a long time ago,
but we're just
seeing it now, right?
Yes. If a star's farther away,
the light takes
longer to reach us.
That's the science.
♪
[DERRIDA] Starlight makes
a long journey across space.
In some cases,
it reaches our eyes
only after hundreds
or even millions of years.
Amazing, huh?
It's like, even though we may
exist in different millennia,
we're still somehow connected
in this moment together,
meeting across time and space.
"Starlight is essentially
a natural time machine." Huh.
[YURI]
Huh? What's that?
[DERRIDA]
Something my father said.
[wind whistling]
[YURI] Why do you
think Mage came here?
[VIDAUX] If we get our hands
on some security footage,
we might find out.
But how would we manage that?
[DERRIDA gasps]
♪
[crackling, wind blowing]
What in the...
Derrida, where are you going?
[wind howling]
[grimace]
[clock ticking slowly]
[laughing]
[continues laughing]
That memory... but why now?
[VIDAUX]
Hey, don't go off alone!
Come back here!
[groan]
Remember...
[crash, rumbling]
[gasp]
[VIDAUX]
Derrida!
Not you again.
-[grunt]
-[slice]
-Get outta here now!
-[BOTH gasp]
[grunt]
[gasp]
[blast]
You're in the way.
I'm just doing my job.
[panting]
Yuri! Are you hurt?
No.
You tell your employer this.
No one gets to Derrida,
except through me.
♪
[chuckle]
[footsteps]
[panting]
-Huh?
-What's wrong?
[YURI]
My camera...
[gasp]
From when you fell earlier?
[sniffle]
You okay?
Yeah. Let's go
and find that footage.
Oh, Yuri.
[wind howling]
[clock ticking slowly]
[JACQUES]
Derrida!
[YOUNG DERRIDA]
Dad!
I'm sorry. I...
I won't run off again,
I promise.
[DERRIDA]
That's right...
When we came here back then,
I got lost, and...
-[footsteps]
-[YURI] Huh?
Hey, where are you going?
[doors opening, hissing]
[YURI]
Is this the security room?
[DERRIDA] We need the monitor
with a memory card.
[YURI]
I'll take a look.
-[beeping]
-If I can just narrow it down
to only locations
where Mage was, then...
[beeping, hissing]
There!
I've copied the footage of Mage.
It's here on this chip.
Great.
I can't believe you just
guessed where it was!
I've actually been here before,
I'd just forgotten!
Huh?
Anyway, let's go!
[gasp]
[YURI]
What now?
-[DERRIDA groaning]
-Are you hurt?
[DERRIDA]
It's no use. I can't go yet.
[YURI]
Uh...
-[air rushing]
-[panting]
♪
[DERRIDA] There's another
important memory here.
[grunt]
[YURI]
Huh?
[panting]
Hey, Derrida, hold on! Wait up!
[footsteps]
[gasp]
No way...
This is the prototype,
the first Automata.
Yes, of course.
That was the day...
My father and I were here.
We came for its
public unveiling.
[electric motors whirring]
Whoa...
[gasp]
[laugh]
[DERRIDA]
That's right.
When I was little,
Dad was nothing short
of a hero in my eyes.
♪
Such an important memory.
How could I have
forgotten it for so long?
[YURI]
"2039.
Automata prototype
commemoration ceremony."
Inventor, Jacques Yvain.
Sorry, Dad.
[grunting]
[crying]
If only I'd
remembered this before.
I was always fighting with him.
And I was too late
to warn him, too.
I...
-[crackling]
-[humming]
[clock ticking slowly]
[gasp]
[ANGE] Feelings at odds
with each other.
Two people's timelines
that never overlapped.
If you could spin
those threads anew...
[ticking]
[energy surging, bang]
[gasp]
[air rushing]
Ah!
[grunting]
[screaming]
[mechanical clicking]
[gasp]
♪
[DERRIDA]
Where am I?
Hmm?
What the...
Can it really be the day
after Mage's birthday?
Could I have time jumped?
[sigh]
Any reply from Jacques Yvain?
[COMPUTER A] Your appointment
today was confirmed.
Meeting site designated.
[sigh]
Dad...
[WOMAN, overlapping]
Clockwise. Anti-clockwise.
[music playing]
[ANNOUNCER]
Welcome to a reinvented world.
[rumbling]
[tires screech]
-[door hisses]
-[car winds down]
I don't have time to
wait for the meeting.
I need to talk to him right now!
Hey, Dad!
You're in there, right?
Open up! It's me, Derrida!
[COMPUTER B]
Retinal scan complete.
-Confirmed. Derrida Yvain.
-[banging]
-[doors slide]
-[panting]
Dad!
He's not here yet.
I need to find him
and tell him about Andrei
as soon as possible.
[COMPUTER C]
How can I help you?
[DERRIDA] What's Jaques Yvain's
current location?
[COMPUTER C]
Location unknown.
GPS is not
currently functioning.
Calendar contains an appointment
with his son this evening.
[DERRIDA]
Huh?
Dad...
♪
[footsteps]
[gasp]
[JACQUES]
You're here already?
Huh?
It's been a while.
How's work been treating
you lately, then?
[DERRIDA] We don't have
any time for small talk.
Listen, you have
to run away with me!
[gasp]
[JACQUES] Andrei's
going to try to kill me?
Yes.
He already knows all
about the DZ bug.
He's going to try
to eliminate us
before we can do
something about it.
I see.
I thought as much.
[DERRIDA]
Huh?
[JACQUES]
Derrida,
you need to get yourself out of
this mess as soon as possible.
Wait, are you telling me
that you already knew
what was going on?
[JACQUES]
Yes, and I also knew that
fixing the bug with a patch
wouldn't make a difference now.
Then you know as well as I do
that we need to get away
from here right now!
[JACQUES]
Absolutely not!
I have a responsibility.
I couldn't do anything
about the buggy DZs,
so I have to see
this through to the end.
No, you can't!
That's crazy talk!
Listen, son.
I wasn't able to make a patch,
but I had a feeling
that you could.
I was right about that,
wasn't I?
[DERRIDA]
Wha?
I knew, it was only
a matter of time
before you surpassed me.
I'm proud of you.
[DERRIDA]
Wha... Y--
You're saying that now?
[JACQUES] That's why the world
can't afford to lose you,
and neither can I.
I don't want to lose my son.
Leave this to me,
and get out of here!
I'll go, but, Dad,
you need to come with me, too!
Those words mean a lot to me.
Thank you.
But you have to go alone.
You must run away and live.
[DERRIDA]
I can't go without you!
I won't let you die for
nothing because of them!
[echoing gasp]
Wait! Dad, no!
[panting]
Dad!
♪
[clock ticking slowly]
[heavy breathing]
[ticking]
-[energy surging]
-[mechanical clicking]
[bang]
I couldn't stop it.
Uh...
Maybe, if I could
just go back...
Remember the past,
all your memories.
If I can just make it
back to Dad!
[sigh]
Derrida?
[heavy breathing, groaning]
Just let me go back
one more time!
I have to get back there!
I finally remembered!
I was going to fix it!
Dad!
[grunt]
[crying]
-[crash]
-[gasp]
-We have to leave, now!
-[crying]
Come on!
-Pull yourself together! [grunt]
-[groan]
I don't know what's
going on with you,
but stop being such a crybaby
and save your tears for later!
We can't afford to die here!
[grunt]
I-I'm sorry.
Huh? Your camera.
Wasn't it broken before?
[YURI]
What are you talking about?
[gasp]
♪
[rumbling, crash]
[debris falling]
[grunt]
[VIDAUX]
Move!
[grunt]
-[grunt]
-[explosion]
-[gasp]
-[screaming]
[crash]
Huh?
[gasp]
[DERRIDA]
You... protected us?
[smash]
-[grunt]
-[bang, clatter]
[VIDAUX]
Don't worry about it!
It was only doing what
it's programmed for!
[grunt]
[blasting, metal shattering]
[gasp]
[glass shattering]
[panting]
[explosion]
[rumbling]
[sigh]
[smash]
[breeze blowing]
Hey, you guys! We're over here!
It's Mayuka!
Hey! Were you driving Graham
without my permission?
It wasn't me,
he drove over by himself!
[GRAHAM]
Affirmative! It was me, Master.
Alright, that's enough.
You're all too damn much.
-[engine roaring]
-[VIDAUX] Let's go.
♪
[debris crumbling]
[grunt]
[GRAHAM]
No enemies detected behind us.
She isn't following.
Did you take any pictures?
[chuckle]
Of course!
Here!
[giggle]
That's so cool!
Oh yeah, Papa, did you find
the thingy you had to get?
[VIDAUX]
Yeah...
Hey, look, that's you!
[YURI]
Wow, snazzy!
Who's the other guy?
[VIDAUX]
My old subordinate.
He died in that city.
His father was a cop, too.
He asked me to retrieve this.
It's the only record left
from when he was alive.
♪
A legacy, he picked
the same career path
as his dad, how nice.
Though he never quite reached
the same heights
that his father did.
Anyway, how did you guys fare?
[YURI] Oh, right!
We have to look at the video!
Yvain.
Jaques.
Derrida.
Look, there!
[YURI]
That's her, but who's she with?
[DERRIDA]
That's...
Cassiel.