[MAGE]
Memory.
♪
The garden where
the tuberoses still bloom.
[breeze blowing]
[gasp]
That’s where I’m waiting.
The mystery of time.
Will it never be solved?
♪
I am waiting for the time,
when you turn back,
and give me the real answer.
♪
[door clanks]
[BOTH panting]
-[YURI] Wait!
-[gasp]
[YURI] If Mage really
is behind this door,
and it turns out that you can
change the world
with a time ride,
then...
♪
[DERRIDA]
Yuri...
I get it. I know.
I know how much you’ve suffered,
just to get here.
I know how sad and painful
it must have been, but...
[YURI crying]
If you change the past,
then all of my memories...
[YURI shudders]
they’ll disappear.
[YURI sobs]
I don’t wanna forget!
Hey...
[YURI] I’ve traveled
all this way with you.
-We’ve been through so much.
-[DERRIDA sighs]
And...
I don’t wanna lose
my memories of this.
None of them,
no matter how small!
Because it’s you, Derrida.
[gasp]
[YURI]
But, I understand.
There’s no future
left for this world.
If I have to give up
my precious memories,
at least it will be so that
everyone can have a future.
That’s what you were
going to say, right?
Yes.
[sniff, chuckle]
Figured, so I thought
I’d beat you to it this time.
Well, let’s go, then!
Yeah.
[gunfire]
[groaning, yelling]
[smashing]
[VIDAUX yelling]
[crash]
-[cases rattling]
-[gunfire]
♪
-[bang]
-[grunt, groaning]
[crackling]
[groaning]
-[MAYUKA] Papa!
-[gasp]
[panting]
[groaning]
Yah!
-[MAYUKA panting]
-Mayuka! Why’re you here?
‘Cause I wanted to be with you!
[VIDAUX sighs]
[gasp]
Stubborn girl.
[whimper]
-[gun clicks]
-[VIDAUX] I’ll protect you,
no matter what!
[gunfire]
[blast]
-Okay, hold on!
-Mm!
[door clicks, whirs]
[door clangs]
[heavy sigh]
[DERRIDA gasps]
♪
♪ Time flows by ♪
♪ A second, minutes ♪
♪ An hour, for eternity ♪
This room...
How could I forget?
[DERRIDA]
It’s a room full of memories.
-[piano playing]
-Huh?
Memories...
[DERRIDA]
Vividness of memory
enhances the time
ride’s precision.
She recreated this room that’s
full of so many memories,
to try to extend
the distance of her jumps.
If that’s true, then...
[YURI]
She must be here!
-Where are you, Mage?
-It’s us!
[footsteps]
[slams door]
♪
♪ There is a colorful path ♪
♪ Which has happened ♪
[YURI]
Mage!
♪ Vividness through
all the motions ♪
This is...
♪ Colors accentuate identity ♪
♪ Time... ♪
[DERRIDA]
Time ride hardware?
[YURI] Derrida!
“To Mage Bilstein.
Be sure to watch this.”
A letter?
Who do you think put it there?
[click, static noise]
-What, Mage?!
-[DERRIDA gasps]
Hi, Mage.
This is your past self.
I’m sure you’re
feeling disoriented.
I’m confused myself, honestly.
I’m leaving this video record,
so that I don’t forget
what’s important.
Did she write
this note herself?
Did she think she’d
forget to watch the video?
Because she knows time
rides erase memories.
That's why.
Don’t forget, what
your ultimate goal is.
Find Derrida Yvain,
-and send him into the past.
-[gasp]
[MAGE]
Even if I can’t do it,
Derrida can.
He can return this world to
the place where it belongs.
It feels so strange to
see my face like this,
reflected on this monitor.
I can’t remember anything
from before I was 14.
I...
managed to perfect
the time ride.
And so I’m losing
memories in exchange.
But there’s one thing
that I do remember.
Derrida.
I need to save Derrida.
I must.
[gasp]
-Please, Ange!
-Wait, Ange?!
Who?
Help me.
Please save Derrida.
[DERRIDA gasps]
[inaudible]
♪
[YURI] What does this mean?
What was she planning?
[DERRIDA]
So, that’s it.
-What is?
-I see now.
Why didn’t I realize it?
Was it Mage who was
making you time ride?
But why? And how?
[DERRIDA]
According to the Trout Theory,
traveling through time requires
significant hardware
to support it.
But, something happened
after I woke from
my 10-year sleep.
I found myself repeatedly
thrust into the past
without the assistance of
any equipment whatsoever.
I thought,
maybe what I was
experiencing was paranormal.
But of course,
that couldn’t be the case.
The hardware was here.
And the time rides were
fed by vivid memories.
Mage created a room
of memories here,
trying to inspire powerful,
vivid recollections.
[YURI] But, Mage couldn’t
travel back to 10 years ago?
[DERRIDA] 10 years was too
far in the past for her.
[YURI]
So, why did she pick you?
For a man who’s been
asleep for 10 years,
it was just like yesterday.
I could go back.
But, how’d she manage to
reach you from so far away?
[DERRIDA gasps]
[chain rattles]
[click]
[disassembling]
[gasps]
♪
It was this!
I didn’t even realize.
But I...
[YURI] Derrida! Do you think
something’s happened to Mage?
[DERRIDA]
Well...
I don’t know how many times
I’ve used this time ride.
And in order to time ride,
you need memories that
can be used as fuel.
[DERRIDA] I wondered why
I wasn’t losing any memories.
I thought maybe I just
couldn’t comprehend
what I’d lost once it was gone.
But now,
I see that was wrong.
The fuel that I was using up
was Mage’s memory.
You mean she was sacrificing
her own memories?
Mage...
Mage.
Wake up, please!
-[wince]
-[BOTH] She moved?!
Who...
[YURI]
It’s me! It’s Yuri!
-Yuri?
-[DERRIDA] Mage.
Hey, it’s me, Derrida!
Derrida?
That’s right!
I finally found you, Mage!
Yeah.
You made it in time, good.
Don’t just
stand there, Derrida.
-Quickly, come inside.
-Inside?
And you too, Yuri. Hurry up.
You’re going to
get covered in snow.
This is that day.
Her eighth birthday.
That’s what she’s seeing now.
-[SCHMIDT] Derrida Yvain!
-[BOTH gasp]
[SCHMIDT]
This is your final warning.
The countdown has begun.
The enemy is poised to
begin obliteration bombing.
Soon, most of our country,
including this place,
-will become an inferno.
-[grunts]
But,
I happen to have some
information on areas
the missile fallout won’t be
able to reach. So, let’s talk.
If you surrender now
and hand over your data,
I will take you someplace safe.
I’ll guarantee your
friends’ lives, too.
Or are you still
under the delusion
that you alone can
save the world?
Don’t make me laugh!
Who do you think you are? God?
Come on out.
Then we can have a toast,
you and I.
To the end of the world!
Damn you.
-[MAGE] Derrida.
-[gasp]
Derrida, please tell me.
Why won’t you help my
dad with his research?
[gasp]
Mage, I...
-[air rushing]
-Derrida.
-[DERRIDA] That’s it.
-[YURI] Huh?
[DERRIDA]
That time.
That place.
The place I should have
gone from the start!
[DERRIDA]
I’m going home.
To the place and the time
that saw this disaster
set into motion.
[SCHMIDT]
What’s the hold up, Yvain?
You’re out of time!
[DERRIDA]
If I don’t go,
she’ll just be waiting in
here like this forever.
♪
That means a time ride?
Yeah.
I understand now that there’s
something I need to say to her.
Once you do, what will happen?
[DERRIDA]
I don’t know, but...
everything’s pointing
to that time and place.
I have to go.
It’s like I said to Donna.
We should fulfill
our obligations
with no fear of failure.
We have no hope of
a future otherwise. Yes.
This will likely be
my final time ride.
It’s dangerous!
But I still have to do it.
At this rate, everything will
be destroyed. Understand?
Me, you, Mage.
Vidaux and Mayuka, too.
Everything and everyone
will be lost!
Mage has been waiting
all this time.
For me.
To finally give
her my real answer.
Hmm.
[machinery powering up]
[click, whir]
[singing]
♪ There is a colorful path ♪
♪ Which has happened ♪
[wind blowing]
♪ Vividness through... ♪
Thank you.
-[young and old YURI sing]
-[DERRIDA] Mage...
This will be my last time ride.
[YURI]
♪ Time goes by ♪
[wind blowing]
[gasp] Hold on!
-Derrida!
-Huh?
I’m off.
[crying]
I’m not going to forget.
[wind blowing]
I won’t forget!
[clock ticking slower]
[energy whining, blasting]
[ANGE]
You’re right.
This really will be
the last time ride, Derrida.
Do you know what you’re going
to do when you get there?
It’s not about actions.
It’s about what I’ll pursue.
It’s about what I’ll hope for!
-[wind blowing]
-[energy whining]
[blast]
[clock ticking faster, stops]
♪
[YOUNG MAGE]
This way! When it warms up,
I wanna plant them right here!
That sounds perfect.
I can’t wait.
-[YOUNG MAGE] Hey, Derrida...
-Huh?
Why...
won’t you help my dad
with his research?
With the time ride?
Humans jumping through time
like that is just a fantasy.
It’s not possible.
[YOUNG MAGE] What is the key to
traveling through time?
To memories that
can’t be erased.
To special times and places.
Why do humans
long to return to moments
they’ve randomly
designated as special?
Wait, Mage?
[chuckle]
You’re amazing.
Not really. I’m quoting
your thesis, that’s all.
Dad completely believes in
the theory that you proposed,
and so do I.
Mage, listen.
It’s just...
[sighs]
[sigh]
Sorry.
I have to apologize to you.
Uh?
[DERRIDA]
For acting in bad faith
with you and your father
when you tried to forward
my Trout Theory research.
Do you mean that--
[DERRIDA] If this is science
that will make people happy,
if it’s something that will
give everyone a future...
then I wanna
have the courage,
and the determination
to pursue it.
Then you’ll help?
Yes. I promise you.
I’ll help you and Nathan
with this research.
[wind blowing]
[DERRIDA]
Yes. This is for the best.
♪
[wind blowing]
[energy humming, whining]
[MAGE]
Dad!
Derrida wanted me
to give this to you!
[gasp]
[DERRIDA] Originally,
Mage tried to run an experiment
that night by
herself and collapsed.
-Then, the next day,
-[inaudible talking]
Nathan took Mage
to the hospital.
[NATHAN]
Mage was doing an experiment.
She’s unconscious.
[beeping]
[answers phone]
[CASSIEL, distorted] I’m
calling to give you a warning.
Who’s this? What warning?
[CASSIEL] It’s up to you
whether to believe it or not,
but it’s extremely important.
Your life may hang
in the balance.
[NATHAN]
Mm. What did you say? Andrei?
Hold on. Do you have proof?
[CASSIEL]
I’m sending encrypted data
directly to your console.
[beeping]
[NATHAN]
This is...
I see. You’re right.
We actually knew about the bug
and have already taken steps.
I have the patch
file right here.
If I act now,
I can probably stop their plan.
I don’t know who you are,
but thank you.
If I hadn’t
gotten your call,
something awful
might have happened.
[DERRIDA] Everything’s
playing out differently?
[wind blowing]
From...
[gasp]
[DERRIDA]
just those few words?
[REPORTER] The exposure by
internal whistle-blowers
of the massive graft
scandal at Rebuild
has resulted in the arrest
of numerous executives
from the company’s
upper echelon.
The ramifications of these
arrests have already started
to show themselves in
neighboring countries,
as government officials
responsible for purchasing
the combat DZs from
Rebuild have been arrested.
And over 10,000 combat DZs,
intentionally programmed
to go berserk,
have been confiscated.
Daddy, what’re
they talking about?
[DAD] It sounds like
the people that were trying
to start a war have been
put in jail, sweetheart.
[giggle]
[YURI]
Oh, okay! That’s good!
[wind blowing]
[DERRIDA]
Ange!
I heard Mage asking you to
help her on that recording.
Who are you?
10 years ago, you died.
Lost to the flames
with Nathan.
Except Mage overwrote
that reality.
Are you serious?
As for me,
I never really existed at all.
The Mage in the world
where you didn’t die...
♪
[gasp]
[ANGE]
Derrida,
do you think the Trout Theory
is something that you created?
[DERRIDA]
Huh?
[ANGE] You merely awoke
it from its slumber.
There is no single
past or future.
It’s like a flowing river,
breaking off into
many directions.
Which branch do you follow?
What end will you reach?
The secret of the Trout Theory
is that by wishing hard enough,
humans can choose.
[wind blowing]
Mage wished
powerfully for a world
in which you and Nathan
didn’t die,
and she just barely managed
to save you, at least.
And then, she entrusted
everything to you.
[DERRIDA]
Mage... saved me?
[ANGE]
That’s right. She saved you,
and then you saved the world.
Out of infinite choices,
that was the only one
that would prevent
wholesale destruction.
And finding the one
river you needed,
you and Mage
made it into reality.
Derrida, never forget
how you feel right now.
It’s not about what you do,
it's about what you hope for.
Follow that path,
and the future will be waiting.
[gasp]
♪
It’s you.
Derrida. Shall we go?
To the world where everything
is back where it belongs.
[energy humming]
[wind blowing]
[bang]
-[car approaching]
-[DERRIDA] Sorry!
I know I’m late again.
Well, you always are.
[DERRIDA]
I gotta make it up to you.
No need! It’s fine.
I knew you’d come
get me eventually,
so all I had to do was wait.
[giggle]
[engine humming]
♪
[MAGE] The ripples in time have
changed a lot of things.
But none of the people here,
existing in this present,
can remember it.
So many possibilities.
All the things that
could have happened.
All the people they
could have met.
[DERRIDA] This version of
the world avoided the war.
That’s all that really matters.
Have Joe and Spencer search
downtown for me, will ya?
I’ll catch up soon.
[MAN] I never really pictured
you as the “dad” kinda guy.
Exciting, huh, “Papa?”
[chuckle]
[DERRIDA] What’s the key
to traveling through time?
Huh? Baby!
Yes, well, pretty soon, anyway!
[MAYUKA]
Do you mind if I feel, miss?
Go ahead.
[DERRIDA] To memories
that can’t be erased.
To special times and places.
Why do humans long
to return to moments,
they’ve randomly
designated as special?
How cute!
[MAYUKA]
That Automata has a ribbon on!
Excuse me, what’s your name?
[GRAHAM]
My name is Graham!
[DERRIDA]
Traveling through time means
tracing back through
your river of memories.
Caring about someone.
Reflecting on yourself
once you’ve reached the end,
the now.
♪
[JACQUES] How’s Derrida’s
research coming along?
[NATHAN] I’m helping
him on my days off,
but there’s not
a lot of progress.
Traveling back in time is
still just an unrealized dream.
Makes sense.
It’s because it’s unrealized
that people are still
pursuing that dream.
[chuckle]
[door opens]
[MAGE] Sorry I’m late!
It was Derrida’s fault.
[YURI]
Tardy again, huh?
You really need to fix
that habit of yours.
-[DERRIDA] Sorry.
-[YURI] Come on, get inside.
-Wait, hold on!
-[BOTH] Huh?
[shutter click]
You two have fun!
-[drip]
-[YURI] Huh?
What the...?
Why do I feel nostalgic looking
at a picture I just took?
[MAN]
Miss Yuri Dietrich?
Could I have
an interview, please?
[gasp]
♪
[MAGE]
We’ll have to start over now.
A new life in a new world.
But somehow, someway,
I’m sure we’ll meet
them all again.
Derrida? Think so?
Of course. I know so.
♪
[DERRIDA] Because as long
as people have hope,
the river will continue to flow,
and the past and the future
will keep being born.