♪
[VIDAUX] Effelsberg
electromagnetic telescope?
Yeah, that’s the “quiet place”
she mentioned.
What is she doing there?
[DERRIDA] She’s continuing
on with our experiment.
[YURI gasps]
But, why?
She’s trying to restore
things to the way they were.
Before the war.
[gasp]
Can she do that?
Isn’t it dangerous, though?
Yes. Which is why
I’m going to stop her.
This was my task
from the beginning.
[YURI gasps]
[YURI]
Derrida, you don’t mean...
[gasp]
[sigh]
I thought you said
that it was impossible
to make major changes.
[DERRIDA] Only if you’re doing
uncontrolled time rides,
in which you don’t know
when or where you’ll
jump to in the past.
If you can control that factor,
then I think,
-it should be doable.
-Hmm...
If you alter the past,
what about us?
Will your time traveling
change who we are today?
Yes, any alterations
I make
could affect
the present as well.
I won’t deny that.
[gasp]
[whimper]
♪
So depending on what you do,
we may no longer be
the people we are right now.
Is our world really
that fragile? Or malleable?
My decisions aren’t all
that matter, though.
The world we live in?
It’s the sum of countless small
choices made by individuals.
[VIDAUX]
I suppose.
I hope even if
the world changes,
I can still remember you guys
and everything
we’ve done together.
[gasp]
Do you really have to go
and change the past, Derrida?
Isn’t there any other way?
I’m sorry, but it’s the only
option available to us now.
[sigh, whimper]
-[beeping]
-Huh?
[GRAHAM] I have just received
an urgent transmission.
[beeping]
The enemy has launched
an obliteration bombing
campaign on our nation.
[ALL gasp]
[GRAHAM]
The target area includes
all land within our borders.
The government is ordering
full retaliation in turn.
[DERRIDA groans]
What does that mean?
[DERRIDA]
Total destruction is imminent.
[clocks ticking]
[one clock ticks louder]
[one clock ticks faster]
[ticking in reverse]
[wind blowing]
♪
[GRAHAM] Detecting a large
number of DZs ahead.
[metal creaking]
[buzz]
[buzzing, creaking, rumbling]
-Let’s go!
-[engine revs]
[tires screech]
-Now!
-[click]
[energy buzzing]
[buzzing continues]
[smash]
[BOTH groan]
[smashing]
[groaning]
Mage came here all by herself?
[gasp]
♪
[engine roaring]
[smash]
[blasting]
[sigh]
Damn scrap heaps!
There you are.
[wind blowing]
Good, they’re not following.
[rumbling]
[wind blowing]
That’s it.
♪
[YURI]
Have you been here before?
[DERRIDA]
Once, when I was a student.
I chose it as
a potential location
for the time jump device.
To use it, you need quiet.
Total quiet.
A place that blocks
electromagnetic waves.
And that’s this place?
She’s here.
I’m sure of it.
[rumbling]
[footsteps]
[gasp]
Behind us!
[grunt, sigh]
[footsteps]
[growl]
Something’s set up
to hold them off.
Mage must be using the device
that she got from Cassiel
to keep the DZs at bay.
Then that’s proof that
she’s definitely here.
But if we continue
any further,
we might not be
able to turn back.
[whimper]
[sigh]
[DERRIDA]
She’ll need to filter out noise.
So I would guess,
she’s down in the basement.
[YURI grunts]
-[MAYUKA] Papa!
-Hmm? What’s up?
Uh. Um...
Well, it’s just...
[VIDAUX]
Hmm...
[MAYUKA sighs]
Mmm...
While we were driving here,
I thought up a story.
When you come back,
can I tell you it?
[gasp]
Yeah.
Course you can, sweetheart.
[whimper]
[rumble]
-[jets humming, air rushing]
-[grunts]
[YURI]
Oh no!
[SCHMIDT laughing on speaker]
[SCHMIDT]
End of the line, you lot!
If you want this to go smoothly,
give yourselves up!
[jets humming]
He found us!
You don’t need Derrida anymore!
[SCHMIDT] That’s where
you’re wrong, Miss Yuri.
With his cooperation,
we’ll have a massive advantage
once the war is over.
No way!
[chuckle]
Guess negotiations broke down.
Release the Xs.
-[KATZE] Yes, sir!
-[chuckle]
[doors open]
[whirring]
[beeping]
♪
What?
[SCHMIDT] Behold! The future
form of the DZs you invented!
They are the true
ultimate weapons!
[DERRIDA]
Those are DZs?!
[chuckling]
-Alright, let’s dance, boys.
-[snap]
[buzzing, whirring]
[YURI whimpering]
[DERRIDA]
Damn.
-Ah!
-[energy buzzing]
[blast]
-[explosion]
-[grunt]
[yell]
[thud, crack]
[gasp]
No good?
Why’d they have to go
and develop these things?
[gunfire]
Charge me extra! Just shoot!
♪
[blasting, explosions]
[gasp]
The device!
[creaking]
[beeping, buzzing]
No!
And right when we were so
close to reaching Mage, too.
[smashing]
[gasp]
[BOTH gasp]
[tires screech]
-[YURI] Mayuka?
-[VIDAUX] What’re you doing?!
[MAYUKA]
It wasn’t me!
Graham just started driving
and told me to get out, I swear!
What?
[GRAHAM]
Master, leave this to me.
I can only do this once,
but I have overclocked
all my functions.
Derrida, I may not exist
in the future that you create.
But, for now...
I must choose the best path.
-[VIDAUX] What do you mean?!
-[gasp]
[GRAHAM]
Master, Mayuka...
It has been a fine journey.
Thank you for all of
the stories you have given me.
-[MAYUKA] Graham!
-[VIDAUX] Wait!
-[engine roar]
-[dust flying]
[engine roar]
[smashing]
♪
[bang, tires screech]
[gasp, growl]
Destroy that thing, now!
[rapid beeping]
[beeping continues to speed up]
[slow beeping]
[explosion]
[ALL gasp]
Oh no, Graham!
-[groaning]
-[metal breaking]
No, please, come back!
-[whimpering]
-[blasting]
-[smash]
-[grunt]
[MAYUKA whimpers]
[VIDAUX]
Derrida, leave this to me.
-Get moving!
-Huh?
-Take her.
-[MAYUKA] Huh?
-Papa...
-I will.
No, you can’t stay!
You have to come, too!
[VIDAUX]
I’ll catch up with you.
[gasp]
Promise me!
♪
[click]
[gun whirs]
They won’t get away!
[laugh]
[beeping]
[gunfire]
-[blasting]
-[groan]
[sigh]
Let’s try this.
[grunt]
-Come on baby, work!
-[hydraulics whir]
-[yelling]
-[firing]
[DERRIDA straining]
[grunting, groaning]
[panting]
No use.
[growling]
We’ll go around.
[breeze blowing]
[YURI gasps]
Mayuka...
Don’t let go of
the hand rail, okay?
Sure!
[wind blowing]
-[machines humming]
-Hmm? [gasp]
[KATZE] Enough of this
foolish resistance!
[HUND]
Come along with us quietly.
[DERRIDA]
C’mon! We gotta run!
[SCHMIDT] Yvain is
the only one we need alive!
Yes, sir.
[blasting]
[YURI]
Ah!
-[gasp]
-[gasp] Yuri!
♪
[heavy breathing]
Just keep going!
Mage is waiting!
What are you saying?
Yuri, you can jump this,
I know that you can!
[SCHMIDT]
Feel free to kill the girl.
Roger that.
Yuri! I’ll catch you!
Dummy, you really
don’t get it, do you?
[beeping]
[YURI]
Okay, here I go!
[gunfire]
[screaming]
[BOTH grunt]
[whirring]
[YURI panting]
-You okay?
-[YURI] Yeah.
Let’s keep moving.
[DERRIDA]
Right.
[gasping]
[GIRLS gasp]
[whirring]
[KATZE]
Derrida Yvain.
There’s no escape,
just surrender.
Damn it all.
We were so close.
[explosion]
[gasp, gurgle]
[slice]
[splatter]
[heavy breathing]
I won’t let anyone...
take it from me.
[gasp]
[DONNA]
I’ll be the one to kill you...
Me!
Donna...
♪
[grunt, growl]
-[footsteps]
-[grunt]
[heavy breathing]
[grunt]
[straining]
Huh?
[DONNA gasping, groaning]
[pained breathing]
[BOTH grunt]
Donna! No, Angelica!
I heard about the experiment.
-[heavy breathing]
-[slice]
I finally understand why
you hate me so much, okay?
[DONNA]
Then answer me this.
Why did you create
something like me?
Something like you?
Answer!
[BOTH grunt]
-[gasp]
-Derrida!
[groaning]
[panting]
-Answer me, Yvain.
-[slice]
Why do humans create
things in their image
that can never be
human themselves?
-[grunt]
-[growl]
Tell me why!
[heavy breathing]
[grunt]
-[thud]
-Ah!
[groan]
You’re saying
Angelica lost her life
because of a worthless
maggot like you?!
[DERRIDA grunt, groaning]
[DERRIDA gasping]
-[coughing]
-[panting]
[DERRIDA]
You’re wrong!
Listen. You are Angelica!
My name is and always
has been Donna!
I’m a mechanical puppet
that you people designed!
Then why do you hate me?
[gasp]
Machines aren’t built to feel.
Automata 2058 may
have called you Donna,
but it wasn’t programmed
to experience any emotions!
[wind blowing]
[2058, voices overlapping]
This is your family...
Get a grip on yourself,
Donna. I am Angelica...
Your panic...
Why wouldn’t I know...
How do you feel about
the name Donna...?
[slice]
Are you saying that...
I’m Angelica? But I...
You are clearly human!
If you were really a machine,
then you wouldn’t have
these emotions!
Impossible!
How dare you lie about this,
when you’re the reason
Angelica is dead!
[DERRIDA]
It’s not a lie!
Try to remember, Angelica!
You are a human being!
Be quiet!
-Ah!
-[splatter]
-[yelp]
-[gasp]
[pained groaning]
[BOTH gasp]
[DONNA screaming]
You’re lying!
[gasp]
Angelica was a pathetic woman
killed during
a simple experiment
she should have been
able to handle!
[gasp]
She and I aren’t the same!
I’m very sorry about
that experiment,
and what it did to you.
-[scream]
-But I promise,
I never meant for anything
like this to happen!
[gasping]
♪
[gasp]
[robotic voice] What else
could it be but Angelica?
[fire crackling]
[gasping]
My name has always been...
Donna.
I am merely a machine,
created by man.
Answer me, Yvain.
Why create things
in your image,
that can never be like you,
no matter how hard they try?
Tell me,
why did you hurt Angelica?
You know,
you’re like me. A scientist.
We do what we do to make
the world a better place.
That’s what your
experiment was, too.
♪
[DONNA]
But you only birthed tragedy.
The price of progress.
If no one had thought
to use science
to give machines personalities,
I could have remained Angelica.
[gasp]
[sigh]
[DONNA]
I see it happening.
I see people like you,
forever creating new things
to satisfy the greed
of those in power.
Glory, prestige,
ambition, pride.
You’ll create anything
for anyone who’ll pay,
never thinking of
how they’ll be used,
or what misery and despair
they’ll bring about.
The advancement of science
can lead to tragedy.
That’s just a risk we take.
But still, if we as a people
stop taking those steps forward,
then all progress stops.
We’d close off our future!
To move forward with that
burden on our shoulders,
that’s what it
means to be human.
♪
[sigh]
So you’ll allow your
egos to lead this world
to ruin on principle.
And I can only watch...
[sob]
[gasp]
[breeze blowing]
[sigh]
[click]
[sighs]
We’re almost there.
Are you sure we
can’t turn back now?
Huh?
[MAYUKA]
But, why?
Derrida, when you do find Mage,
you’ll go back in time
and change the world?
Yeah.
[YURI] And once it’s changed,
all this will be gone!
[YURI gasps]
Are you okay with that?
I have no way to know
if this is right.
But, if I don’t do it,
I’ll always regret it.
So, I must.
[sigh]
-[groan]
-[door opens]
[YURI]
Huh? Mayuka?
Aren’t you coming with us?
Come on now.
[sigh]
Big Sis, you go on.
I've decided that I’m
gonna go back to Papa.
[YURI]
Huh?
If the world's gonna
change no matter what,
then I wanna stay with Papa
until everything goes poof!
Mayuka...
♪
Be careful, okay?
Hmm?
Mm-hmm!
Bye-bye, Derrida, Yuri!
I believe in you!
-[door closes]
-[YURI gasps, sighs]
[sigh]
[panting]
[elevator rumble]