♪
[DERRIDA] The war’s become
even more devastating.
Everywhere you look,
we’re on a path to destruction.
Is this...
a result of me
changing the past?
-[cameras flashing]
-What now?
[grunt]
What can I do?
What should I do?
[wind blowing]
[VIDAUX]
Where do you think this
“quiet place” is that
Cassiel mentioned?
[groaning]
[DERRIDA]
I don’t know yet.
But I do have a place in mind
that could be a possibility.
Huh? What’s that?
[DERRIDA]
Yetz Engineering College.
It’s my alma mater.
(engine starts up)
(engine humming)
[DERRIDA]
Mage...
Why are you researching
the Trout Theory?
It’s flawed and dangerous.
If I’d listened back then
instead of simply refusing you,
could we have avoided
this whole thing?
I swear...
I’ll find you soon.
♪ ♪
[engines humming]
[GRAHAM] Suspicious behavior
from vehicles behind us.
-Number?
-[GRAHAM] Four detected.
[YURI]
Mayuka, stay hidden.
-[gunfire]
-[DERRIDA, YURI scream]
[VIDAUX]
Mouth shut, remember?
[tires screeching]
[gasp, grunt]
[BOTH scream]
[engines roaring]
-[gunfire]
-[tires screech]
-Autopilot!
-[GRAHAM] Roger.
[beep]
[gunfire]
-Ahh!
-[gunfire]
[explosion]
-[yelling]
-[gunfire]
[whimpering]
[clicking, whirring]
[tires screeching]
Ah!
[explosion]
-[tires screech]
-[explosion]
[GRAHAM] The two vehicles
behind us are closing in.
Safe route determined.
Leave the highway,
enter the mountain roads,
and at the first curve,
drive off the edge
into the forest below.
Hold on!
How’s that safe, exactly?
[YURI] You’re telling us
to drive off a cliff?
[GRAHAM] My reinforced
plating can endure it.
[grunt]
[tires screech]
[engine roars]
[engines roar]
Everyone, prepare for impact!
[smash]
[BOTH groan]
[grunting]
♪ ♪
[DERRIDA]
No sign of pursuit.
[sighing]
We’ll wait it out
here until morning.
[DERRIDA]
Yeah. Sounds good.
[GRAHAM]
After weighing all outcomes,
this was the most
optimal choice available.
Hey, you okay?
Hmm! Yeah, I’m good!
-[VIDAUX panting]
-[BOTH gasp]
[grunt]
[MAYUKA]
Papa, you’re bleeding!
[DERRIDA]
We need to treat him, now.
No, it’s nothing. I’m fine.
Just stings a little.
[DERRIDA]
You’re definitely not fine!
[sigh]
Where’s the medical kit in here?
[YURI]
Move aside, let me handle it.
[water flowing]
[insects chirping]
[groaning, wincing]
I’ll work quickly.
Yeah. Alright.
[VIDAUX sigh, wincing]
[groaning continues]
Papa...
[insects chirping]
Wonder if there’s any
fresh water nearby.
[MAYUKA]
Is Papa going to be alright?
Mmm.
We just have to wait for
the medicine to kick in.
He needs to lie still
for a while, that’s all.
[chuckle]
Okay!
That’s good, then!
[sigh]
Hey, what’s wrong?
Are you still worried?
I swear, it’ll be okay.
Mmm.
Huh?
[VIDAUX groans, sighs]
[gasp]
[DERRIDA]
So many scars.
If it weren’t for
the war, maybe...
♪
[DERRIDA]
Vidaux.
Hmm?
Listen,
wouldn’t it be better to drop
off Mayuka somewhere safe?
[VIDAUX]
Hmm?
[DERRIDA] I know it’s
dangerous everywhere, but...
there must be someplace
better than with us.
Like back with that mechanic
friend of yours, Klaus.
[VIDAUX] And you really
think she’ll be safe there?
No, not totally. But still, I--
[VIDAUX] If you’re going to
lecture me, you can leave.
I’m sorry.
[rock bounces]
♪
[MAYUKA]
Papa never keeps himself safe.
[YURI] But if it weren’t
for him, the rest of us
wouldn’t have made it this far!
I’m grateful.
Yeah...
[YURI]
Mayuka,
would you like it if you had
more time to play with him?
Huh?
Hmm...
Yeah! Why wouldn’t I?
Did you get to play
with your papa?
Mmm.
My dad’s actually the one who
taught me about photography.
We’d go out
and take pictures together.
You’re so mature for your age.
Do you ever get lonely?
[MAYUKA]
Hmm...
Sometimes, but at least
I have my books.
When Papa’s off doing stuff,
I always have stories
to keep me company.
♪
Reading books,
I can imagine all
kinds of things.
And when a page is missing,
I make up what happened!
Sometimes Papa doesn’t come
back for two or three days,
so I have lots of time to think
about the stories I’ve read.
When I grow up, I’ll put them
together and be a writer!
[laugh]
That’s great!
[MAYUKA]
I wanna be a good writer
and make lots of money for Papa.
I’m only here because of him,
so I need to do what I can.
♪
Well, I’ll be your first fan!
-I promise.
-[MAYUKA giggles]
[MAYUKA]
Is that a firefly?
[YURI]
Huh? Oh, it is!
[gasp]
I’ve never seen
real ones before!
[gasp]
[giggle]
[shutter snapping]
-[snap]
-[MAYUKA gasps]
-[MAYUKA giggles]
-[footsteps]
-[giggle]
You all done?
Huh?
Yeah.
[sigh]
-[DERRIDA] I made Vidaux upset.
-Huh?
You couldn’t bandage
him up right?
It’s not that.
It’s about Mayuka.
-Huh?
-It’s not my place,
but I’m worried that
she isn’t safe with us.
You’ve got a point.
I’m no dad,
but should you really take
your kid everywhere with you,
-even if it’s dangerous?
-Well, I mean...
It’s weird,
but I assumed
there was a reason.
Something that we just
don’t understand.
[MAYUKA humming]
[DERRIDA]
A reason...
[YURI] I don’t know
what it could be, though,
or if it’s any
of our business.
[groaning]
[MAN] Inspector Vidaux
has it under control.
He’s arrested the culprit!
You’re doing truly
incredible work out there.
It’s nice to know I have
a man in the field
I can always count on.
[thud]
♪
All that guy cares about is
getting good press for himself.
What a freakin’ joke!
You’re telling me!
I can’t stand him.
Never responds to
our calls for backup,
but he’s always there to
take the credit, isn’t he?
Don’t be concerned
with that crap.
Our job is to catch bad guys,
and see that they’re punished.
That’s all that matters.
Yeah, I mean... I guess so, sir.
-[phone vibrates]
-Uh--
[sigh]
Hello?
[gasp]
[COP]
Inspector!
[OFFICIAL] Regulations forbid
you from working on a case
that involves your own family.
[heavy breathing]
♪
[REPORTER] A week has passed
since the hit-and-run incident,
but still no suspects
have been identified...
The law is bullshit.
And justice is bullshit, too.
[VIDAUX] And neither of
them could protect my wife.
An eye for an eye.
A tooth for a tooth.
The fate of all
sinners is punishment.
♪
[lock creaks]
[cocks gun]
Let me teach you
this world’s rules.
An eye for an eye.
A tooth for a tooth.
And so it follows...
[gunshot]
that for a death a death.
[baby crying]
Huh?
[continues crying]
[gasp]
[sigh]
[crying continues]
That bastard Derrida.
Making me relive
those awful memories.
-[beeping]
-What is it, Graham?
[GRAHAM] Several armed machines
are rapidly approaching.
[grunt]
[GRAHAM]
DZs.
[sigh]
[WOMAN, overlapping]
Clockwise. Anti-clockwise.
♪
[DERRIDA]
What’s wrong?
[VIDAUX]
DZs, incoming.
[sigh]
We’ll head out
before they’re on us.
[DERRIDA]
Mm-hmm.
[engine humming]
Hmm...
[buzzing]
[DERRIDA]
Maybe 20 of them?
No, it looks like
even more than that.
[VIDAUX] What do you think?
Another DZ graveyard?
[air rushing]
[thud, crunch]
So, what’ll we do?
[VIDAUX growls]
What do you think?
We plow through!
Ah!
[engine roars]
[gunfire]
[tires screeching]
[tires screech]
[engine roars]
[groan]
[grunt]
Whoa!
-[bang]
-[whine]
[gunfire]
[buzzing, hissing]
♪
Ahead of us, too?
[gasp]
Damn junk!
[gunfire]
Graham! Any other weapons?
[beeping]
What the--?
[DERRIDA]
You take the front!
[gunfire]
[explosion]
-[explosion]
-[smash]
Got it!
Don’t celebrate!
There’s more coming!
[DERRIDA]
I gotcha!
-[gun clicking]
-[gasp]
Derrida, take this!
Thanks. Watch Mayuka!
Pretty cocky. Be careful!
You’ll get yourself hurt.
Don’t you worry about me,
I’m here to watch your back!
-[blast]
-[explosion]
[hissing]
[GRAHAM]
Now there are approximately 20.
-What? Still that many?
-[whining]
Damn it!
-[blasting]
-[gunfire]
-[hissing]
-[thud]
[gasp]
-[crunch]
-[grunt]
[groaning]
No, Vidaux!
-[smashing]
-[grunting]
Papa, no!
[MAYUKA]
Come back...
Come back, Papa!
[buzzing, hissing]
[groaning]
Damn. Not good.
[slice]
Vidaux fell off!
We have to go back!
Hurry! Save Papa, please!
-Graham, do it!
-[GRAHAM] Do what?
Go back! Right now! Save Papa!
[GRAHAM]
Roger that!
[engine roar]
[tires screech]
[wind blowing]
[VIDAUX]
The truth is,
I could've let her
go at any time.
I told myself that
nowhere was safe enough.
But, the real reason is...
-[MAYUKA] Papa!
-Huh?
-Get out of the way!
-[gasp]
[engine roaring]
[smash, thud]
Duck, Vidaux!
[gunfire]
[explosions]
[whining]
♪
[screaming]
[explosions]
[smash]
[thud]
[heavy breathing]
It’s over.
[wind blowing]
[grunting]
You kids really don’t know
how to play gentle, do you?
If you’re going to lecture me,
then you can leave.
Hmm...
[chuckle]
[water running]
♪
-[splash]
-[gasp]
-[YURI] Here. Take it.
-Huh?
-Thank you.
-[giggle]
[footsteps]
[MAYUKA]
Papa!
You okay, sweetheart?
[MAYUKA]
Yep. Thanks to you!
How about you though?
Oh, I’m fine.
Couldn’t be better.
But it’s thanks to you,
this time.
[giggle]
Mayuka,
don’t you ever do anything
like that again, alright?
Aww!
Oh, I forgot!
I found something earlier
that I wanted to show you!
[giggle]
Aren’t they pretty?
They are. That’s for sure.
But, Mayuka,
you should let them go.
Hmm?
Well, they can’t stay
in your hands forever,
now can they?
Huh?
♪
No, I guess not.
Bye-bye!
Hmm?
[BOTH laugh]
[VIDAUX]
Okay. Let’s take a short break,
then head out again.
-[VIDAUX strains]
-[MAYUKA yelps]
-Papa, are you okay?
-[chuckle]
I can handle you easily, kid.
Huh?
I’ll be heavier
next year, though.
And I’ll be even bigger and
taller the next one after that!
But Papa can carry me.
Papa is strong.
[chuckle]
-[VIDAUX grunts]
-[MAYUKA yelps]
[BOTH laughing]
Yuri, what we were
talking about earlier...
Uh-huh. I get you.
They’re a good family,
aren’t they?
[shutter snaps]
[DERRIDA]
Yeah.
-[high-pitched whine]
-Huh?
[jet engines roar]
[DERRIDA]
Are those...
No, can it be?
[air raid siren]
[explosions]
[MAN]
It has begun.
♪
There’s no way.
I can’t allow this!
I need to time ride again!
-I need to change the pa--
-[gasp]
[ANGE] The time ride
is not all-powerful.
Changes to any given past
event can only be made once.
[DERRIDA]
Every time I go back,
I further limit my chances of
actually changing anything.
Wait a minute.
My memories...
Is this memory even reliable?
If I’m losing memories
because of the time rides,
then wouldn’t that mean...?
[heavy breathing]
I don’t feel like
I’m missing anything.
But, if I had lost my memories,
would I even realize it?
♪
[WOMAN]
Sorry for the wait.
Are you the one who
wanted to speak with me?
[MAGE] It’s been quite a while,
Professor Marlene.
Uh?
We two met at my
father’s funeral,
or don’t you remember?
I’m Mage Bilstein.
[PROFESSOR]
Ah. Nathan’s girl.
[MAGE]
Please, Professor.
Teach me about
the Trout Theory.
I need to understand it.
I’m sorry, Mage.
But that is still
an unproven theory, you know.
Accompanied by many unresolved
and dangerous issues.
And even if it could
be utilized as intended,
it consumes incredible
amounts of fuel.
Are you certain you want to jump
back, knowing all of that?
I do,
because I need to.
There’s no other way.