[MAGE]
Yuri...
♪
I'm sorry for running
off on my own.
But...
I know that we'll meet again.
Thanks for everything.
I love you.
-[DERRIDA] Mage...
-[click]
She disappeared one day.
This is all she left me.
[VIDAUX]
If the reason they're after her
is because of the access key
to the patch file you gave her,
[footsteps]
why don't you just make another
one and sell it off already?
It's not that simple.
I'd need equipment,
not to mention the time!
So, it seems, you were lying
when you said that brain
of yours
would be worth something to me.
I know there are people
who'd want the key!
Wait, hang on a second.
What ever happened to Rebuild?
They haven't been blamed
for all this destruction?
[VIDAUX] [sigh]
Exactly the opposite.
The government brought them
in to stop the rampaging DZs,
and now they're positioned as
the country's largest
defense contractor.
[DERRIDA]
No...
[VIDAUX] Pursuing a case
against Rebuild would make
the government liable as well,
since they're the ones
that commissioned them
in the first place.
Of course they can't
swallow that pill,
so they've let the issue
languish while the war drags on.
-Damn it.
-Hey!
Speaking of Rebuild!
If we accept that
Derrida's story is true,
then the people most
interested in the patch file,
would be Rebuild
and the government.
Yeah, that's right.
Then it stands to reason
that Rebuild has some leads
on where to find Mage!
[gasp]
♪
[DERRIDA] We can't use
the internet? You're kidding.
[VIDAUX]
Don't know what to tell you,
the war's trashed
our infrastructure.
Hardly anywhere except the
city center has a connection.
[DERRIDA sighs]
[DERRIDA] So, our only option
is infiltrating Rebuild
and using their terminals
to steal the data
from the network directly.
[VIDAUX] There's one
problem with that, too.
[DERRIDA]
Of course there is. What is it?
[VIDAUX] Das Band.
A wall meant to keep refugees
from the city's
war-torn outskirts
from pouring into
the inner limits.
[DERRIDA] All this happened in
the 10 years I've been asleep.
What should we do?
Is there any way to get inside?
[footsteps]
[DERRIDA]
Seems so obvious.
Is it safe?
[VIDAUX] There are some nasty
rumors about this place.
[BOTH grimace]
[DERRIDA]
Care to elaborate?
[rubble crunching]
♪
[grunt]
[sigh]
[groan]
-[squeak]
-[BOTH gasp]
[DERRIDA]
Hey.
You still haven't
answered my question.
I dunno.
Might've been a gas leak
or a cave-in,
but people keep dying in here
and repairs end up stalling.
So...
Oh no. It's not...
a ghost, is it?
[VIDAUX] I wish it was
something that whimsical.
Tell ya what, though,
since I'm feeling generous,
I won't charge extra for this.
[DERRIDA] Are you really
talking about my tab right now?
[VIDAUX]
I told you.
I don't work for free.
[YURI] Come on!
So if someone's in trouble,
but they don't have any money,
you'd abandon them?
[VIDAUX]
Yeah.
It's not my job to
be a bleeding heart.
Doesn't your conscience
ever bother you?
Conscience?
I don't trust
something like that.
Wow, seriously?
[DERRIDA sighs]
-I'll make money, or rather...
-Huh?
There's a man named Andrei.
10 years ago, he killed my
father and framed me for it.
If I can expose him
and clear my name,
I should get my position back,
and all of the money
that's rightfully mine.
I swear,
no matter what,
I'll be sure he pays
for what he's done.
[sigh]
[breeze humming]
[water dripping]
[running water]
[VIDAUX] This should put us
on the other side of the wall.
Now, let's look for a way
to the surface.
-But how are we supposed to fi--
-[MAYUKA whines]
[yelp]
-Huh?
-Hmm?
[gasping]
Hey!
-[MAYUKA] What?
-Next to that pillar,
I saw someone,
-a shadow!
-[flashlight clicks]
[MAYUKA]
Was it a ghost?!
There! See it? Right there?
[panting]
♪
[creaking]
[MAYUKA and YURI screaming]
Hmm...
[VIDAUX] [sigh]
I thought so.
This place is infested!
Wait! Turn off the lights,
-and cut the engine, too.
-What, why?
[DERRIDA]
It's a low battery warning.
The way their eyes are blinking
means they're in emergency mode.
-[VIDAUX] Shut down the engine.
-[GRAHAM] Roger.
[VIDAUX]
Explain, Derrida.
Sleep mode. They're out of fuel,
so they can't move.
[BOTH whimpering]
But they reacted to the light,
so their sensors aren't dead.
It's like they're on standby,
preserving every bit
of battery they can
in order to keep monitoring
their surroundings,
and so they can counterattack
if there's hostile stimuli.
If we don't trigger
those sensors,
we should be able to pass.
[VIDAUX]
You sure about this?
If I was programming
them for militarization,
that's what I would've done.
[VIDAUX]
Okay, Graham.
Shut down all sensors.
Nice and quiet, now.
[rubble crunching]
[DERRIDA]
Just how many are there?
[BOTH whimpering]
[crunch, smash]
[gasp]
[DZs humming, creaking]
[whimpering, gasp]
[air rushing, thud]
[BOTH gasp]
♪
[gasping]
[humming continues]
So, it comes down
to a fight anyway!
[tires screeching]
[smash]
[groaning]
[grunt]
[humming]
[blast]
[thud]
[tires screeching]
[crash]
[electronics winding down]
[beeping]
[VIDAUX] Looks like you
were right, Derrida.
They didn't pursue us
through the passageway.
[YURI] But, there'll be
more at the next station.
Don't worry.
We should be able to take
the construction workers'
stairway up.
[VIDAUX]
Hey, what about Graham?
You suggesting
we leave him here?
[GRAHAM] I cannot endorse
this plan of action.
No, not at all.
We'll take Graham with us, too.
[footsteps]
[DERRIDA]
Everything's ready.
[VIDAUX]
I don't like this.
♪
[MAYUKA]
Hello! Hello!
Testing, testing!
[YURI]
Can you guys hear us?
-Loud and clear, very good.
-Hmm?
Now, Graham,
maximize the broadcast strength
and encryption. You got it?
[GRAHAM]
Roger that, sir.
Huh! Was that actually
Graham's voice?
-[GRAHAM] It's remote access.
-[VIDAUX] Hmm...
I told you we'd be bringing him.
Having a good A.I. on our side
will make this
easier to pull off.
-[growl]
-[GRAHAM] Much appreciated.
Hey! Don't use Graham in
ways that I don't understand!
Why not? It's a basic feature.
Hey, Graham. Map, please.
[beeping]
[GRAHAM]
Acquiring data about
Rebuild's staff
and security placement,
using internal attendance
tracking system.
Everyone's gone home.
Looking good.
-Yeah, what makes you so sure?
-[chuckle]
That's the benefit
of being former staff.
If we use a fake pass
like this one,
then even if the security robots
see us, they won't bother us.
[VIDAUX] You seem awfully
familiar with all this.
[DERRIDA] One of the first
things I did when I got hired
was rig the time card system.
I didn't want my work schedule
to be decided by some machines.
Ah. I thought you were
a goodie-two-shoes type,
but you had a real bad streak.
-I'm impressed.
-Maybe.
It just made me mad how they'd
force me out at quitting time,
even if I wanted
to work all night.
[VIDAUX]
Huh?
[beeping]
[doors slide open]
You don't have to
keep looking around.
There's no one here.
And this will fool the machines!
Based on your memories
from 10 years ago, at least.
Security is even lighter
than I remember, actually.
Even the guard's office
has been moved
to the weapons
department floor.
Guess this company really
is a defense contractor now.
[DERRIDA]
Andrei...
[elevator humming]
[beep]
So, this Andrei guy,
what if he turned out to be
in the building right now?
Huh?
As if he would ever
stay this late.
I'm talking hypothetically.
If the man who killed
your best friend
and your father
were here right now,
what would you do?
Well, I...
[VIDAUX]
I should make it clear,
I won't take part in revenge.
Not for any reason.
If you're in this
to get vengeance,
I'm pulling out here and now.
♪
Another regulation of yours?
No, more serious than that.
It's a belief
I refuse to compromise.
[DERRIDA] Even if the vengeance
would be righteous?
Derrida.
If you really believe
that there's such a thing
as perfectly
righteous revenge,
when the time comes,
find a mirror.
[DERRIDA]
A mirror?
[VIDAUX]
Look at your face, that's all.
[beep]
♪
Okay, let's split up.
I'll start by hitting
the executive suite.
Yeah, okay.
I'll check out my old lab,
it's just up ahead.
[DERRIDA] We'll meet
at the elevator in 20.
[VIDAUX]
Right.
[door opens]
[door closes]
Nobody wanted
a murderer's old lab?
I guess I understand that.
[computer whirring]
[typing]
A password?
That's pretty old-school.
His last login was on...
December 20th, 2050.
That day.
"Happy birthday."
[clicking, creaking]
[beeping]
What kind of flower
did she like, again?
♪
Mage...
Take care... of Mage!
[gasp]
[groaning]
[mechanical tick]
[gasp]
It's you again.
My name is Ange.
[WOMAN, overlapping]
Clockwise. Anti-Clockwise.
♪
[DERRIDA]
Who are you?
What's going on?
You're not Mage.
[ANGE]
Mage is waiting for you.
She's been waiting a long time.
[heavy breathing]
[DERRIDA]
I have to kill Andrei.
I don't have time to hesitate.
At this rate, Dad, Nathan,
and Mage will be...
Do it! This is
the only right choice.
[heavy breathing]
[VIDAUX]
Look at your face.
[heavy breathing]
[wind swirling]
[painful groaning]
Ah!
What the--
What was I just doing?
I was on my way to
the flower shop...
[gasp]
[crackling, beeping]
That was...
-[door opens]
-[gasp]
It's time, what're you doing?
[gasp, grunt]
I copied every file that
they had even vaguely
relating to Madge Bilstein.
What about you?
Sorry, I'm on it now.
Well, hurry up!
I'll go stand watch.
[growl]
[click, typing]
[DERRIDA]
This file...
Nathan had an information
source I didn't know about.
Is that what
the password was for?
This is...
It... can't be!
-[YURI] Someone's coming!
-Huh?
Looks like a human
security force. Run!
Company!
We can't use the elevator.
Let's take the security stairs!
[panting]
[DERRIDA]
The alarms aren't sounding!
They don't know we're here yet!
[panting]
Just eight more floors and
we can get out into the park.
We'll meet up with Graham
and make a plan.
Yuri, if you're not
sure about driving,
now's the time to speak up.
[YURI]
Leave it to me!
That car's too conspicuous!
We've managed to not make any
electronic footprints so far!
If we just wait a while...
All well and good,
but somebody left
non-electronic footprints
on that dusty lab
floor upstairs.
[heavy breathing]
[alarm blaring]
-[bang]
-Damn it!
I'll overlook a few
scratches on the car,
so just gun it over here!
♪
-[roar]
-[MAYUKA] Got it!
Okay, let's hit it!
So, this is what
a steering wheel feels like.
Huh?
How's it start?
[tires screeching]
[metal scraping]
[swoop, thud]
[tires screeching]
You told Papa that you
were sure you could drive!
Mmm!
[YURI] I'm definitely getting
my license this year!
He told us to gun it, remember?
I'm coming, Derrida.
Hang in there.
You really like him, huh?
You guys would be cute together!
Huh, what's that?
Can't hear you!
[doors slamming]
[DERRIDA panting]
[gunshots]
[grunt]
♪
[gunfire]
[explosion]
[panting]
Almost!
[tires screeching]
Get ready to jump, Derrida!
Huh?
[grunt]
[air rushing]
-[tires screeching]
-[banging]
[thuds, grunts]
[smash]
[buzzing, humming]
Yahoo!
-[camera snap]
-[giggle]
-Take your wall and shove it!
-[camera snap]
[camera snap]
[gasp]
Derrida?
[VIDAUX]
That was rough.
What a crazy ride.
[snoring]
Any luck finding out
where Mage might be?
[VIDAUX]
Not yet.
But hopefully we'll be able
to find something
in this mountain of files
we took from Rebuild.
That's great, it means
there's a chance!
Isn't that right, Derrida?
Uh. Hey, what's wrong?
Well, it...
It's good news about Mage, yeah.
But...
[typing]
-[YURI] Hmm?
-[VIDAUX] Hmm.
[gasp]
[DERRIDA]
I thought that it was Andrei,
who was behind
the incident 10 years ago.
That he was trying
to kill off people
who knew about the DZ bug,
to keep the secret hidden.
[YURI]
But, it wasn't?
[DERRIDA]
That data shows
that the DZ bug
was manufactured
and put in there
intentionally.
-But, why?
-How do you know this?
[DERRIDA] It's signed by all
the executives except my father.
Government officials, too.
That can only mean...
the DZ rampage was engineered
by the government
and Rebuild from the start.
I don't understand.
When the DZs went haywire,
it turned the war
completely upside down.
He thinks it was
done on purpose,
by people who stood to
benefit from the chaos.
No way.
♪
[DERRIDA]
The patch file I made,
they don't need it at all.
They'd actually prefer
to be rid of it!
[DERRIDA]
It isn't just Rebuild
who's after the access key
for the patch.
It's the government,
and the other countries
involved in the war, too.
[sigh]
Vidaux.
It's time we parted ways.
I won't drag you
any deeper into this.
I'll pay you the money
I owe you, I promise.
Could you just take Yuri
somewhere safe for me?
Derrida!
[DERRIDA] It was my misplaced
optimism that caused this mess!
Wait, hold on!
It isn't only your fault.
I also...
Yuri?
So, what's your plan?
I need to find Mage first,
no matter what.
Then, I wanna do
something about
this endless gridlock of a war!
Hmm...
When a man discovers something
more valuable than his revenge,
he's earned my assistance.
[gasp]
[sigh]
Oh, is that so?
Another of your regulations?
No sir.
Spur of the moment choice.
I actually got a copy
of your data, too.
You have quite a fortune,
based on patents alone.
Once we've got
your name cleared,
I'll accept all
of it as payment.
♪
[MAN 1]
So then,
do we have a final report
on the rampaging Automata?
Anyone?
[MAN 2] We've concluded
it is no longer possible
to settle the situation
through normal methods.
[MAN 3]
Pandora's box is open,
and there's no way
to close it, then.
That's what you're saying?
[typing]
♪
Huh?
[footsteps]
-You thinking?
-Yeah.
I had a dream about
Mage's birthday.
Thing is, in the dream,
I was...
[chuckle] Well, it would've made
me late, so it's impossible.
You mean her birthday
party 10 years ago?
But, you were late that day.
Huh?
I mean, you got there
after I did, at least.
[click]
Hmm...
[MAGE]
Coming!
[doors creak]
You're late, Derrida!
-[splat]
-[gasp]
[YURI laughing]
[DERRIDA]
Uh, happy birthday, Mage!
Did I...
change things...
with a time ride?
Did I experience
a different past?
♪
[DERRIDA]
Uh, happy birthday, Mage!
[laughing]
It's not that funny,
stop laughing!
[gasp]