[humming, whirring]
[gasp]
[DERRIDA]
What the hell?
[DERRIDA breaths heavily]
[DERRIDA shouts]
[DERRIDA pants]
[pants]
--[buzzing]
--[DERRIDA gasps]
Huh? Hey!
--[footsteps]
[VIDAUX]
Guess you're too locked up.
Then I've got no choice...
[DERRIDA]
What the hell is going on here?
Listen! Where am I?
--Who are y--
--Would you shut up?
[DERRIDA]
Please tell me, when is this?
[VIDAUX]
Who really gives a crap?
It's winter all
year 'round, anyway.
[DERRIDA] What the...?
Hey, what year is it?
[VIDAUX]
2060.
Hmm, wrong one.
That means that I've traveled
10 years into the future?
I was... framed.
Someone set us up!
I was driving away with Nathan,
and then after that...
That's right! I fell into
a cryostasis chamber!
Huh? Cryostasis?
They outlawed that
procedure back in the day
'cause of constant malfunctions.
What happened here?
[VIDAUX]
Obvious, ain't it? A war.
There's no way...
[VIDAUX]
Believe it.
And it's all thanks to these
damn puppet soldiers.
[DERRIDA]
DZs...
[MAN]
Early in the war,
these mindless hunks of
junk were all the rage.
The latest weapon.
The men who made them
got filthy rich.
Wish I could see
the bastards' faces.
[DERRIDA]
Uh, wait a sec!
--[VIDAUX] What'll you pay me?
--[DERRIDA] Huh?
Walking around alone out here,
a guy like you won't
even make it 100 meters.
If I offer you protection
and transport to somewhere safe,
how much will you pay?
[DERRIDA]
Hey, the other ones are coming!
[VIDAUX]
Better decide quick.
Going rate's 200.
[DERRIDA]
What?
[VIDAUX]
Too rich for your blood?
That's the price of your life.
[DERRIDA]
Alright, fine! I'll pay!
The name's Vidaux.
--[cocks gun]
--[DERRIDA gasps]
--[VIDAUX] C'mon.
--[DERRIDA gasps] Huh?
[MAYUKA gasps]
Huh?
[VIDAUX]
Mayuka!
[MAYUKA]
Papa!
[VIDAUX] Didn't I tell you
to stay inside the car?
[MAYUKA]
Mmm.
[MAYUKA sighs]
Hi, come in.
Hi. Who's she?
[VIDAUX]
Don't waste time, just get in!
Raise us up, Graham, gotta go.
[GRAHAM] Engaging
four-wheel independence.
Activating fenders.
Extract the fee
from our guest, Mayuka.
It's 200.
[MAYUKA]
Mmm.
I'm not picking up a chip.
[VIDAUX]
What? That's impossible.
[GRAHAM] Perhaps it is
an older model of chip.
Try using the terminal
on the side, Mayuka.
'Kay.
What do you mean by a chip?
Huh? You don't know?
[VIDAUX] He said he's
been asleep for 10 years.
One hell of a nap.
[GRAHAM]
Survivor ID not found.
What?
Whoa! Hold on, mister!
You're not dead, are you?
Huh?!
[VIDAUX] There's more
of 'em. We'll talk later!
[grunts]
[BOTH gasp]
[GRAHAM]
Fasten seat belts.
Hunks of scrap metal.
[BOTH groaning]
[VIDAUX]
Brace yourselves!
[BOTH groaning]
[ALL grunting]
Papa! Graham's gonna
get hurt! Be careful!
[GRAHAM]
Major damage to rear mechanics.
[VIDAUX] More of 'em. And these
have got rocket launchers?!
[VIDAUX]
Woo!
There's a few of those
treasures still floatin' around?
Gotta come back for those later.
[ANDREI]
Yes, perfect.
The eighth wave of
additional government funding
will be approved next month.
Keep production firing
on all cylinders, okay?
No, no, no! Certainly not!
I'll need you to show
a bit of restraint
when it comes to that,
my friend.
Maintaining a balance of power
is the key to everything
in this game, after all.
Oh, no, not that!
That's a different
matter entirely!
[laughs]
Well, you've definitely
got me there, I suppose!
Very good!
Well, see you later!
[sigh] This "nicey-nice"
stuff's aggravating.
I'm fed up with
this nonsense already!
Oh, look at the time,
didn't even notice.
I'm going to be late to the
party if I don't hurry.
Lily! My things.
[LILY]
Certainly.
[DZ] Sir, there is a matter
requiring your action.
Oh, Marie. Please, not now.
Shoo. I'm running quite behind,
and there's nothing
more important than a party.
[MARIE] I'm afraid it's of
prime importance, sir.
Listen here.
There's nothing in that
two-bit robot brain of yours
that could possibly be...
[gasp]
[MARIE]
Derrida Yvain.
His life signature was
detected yesterday.
[ANDREI]
Impossible. He should be...
[gasp] No, there's no way!
Derrida is still alive?!
But no one has seen or heard
from him in 10 years!
That man is supposed to be dead!
[MAYUKA]
I'm starving.
Sorry. I'm flat broke.
Stop sulking.
[DERRIDA] I don't get it.
What's going on here?
[MAYUKA]
Dinner, Papa.
[VIDAUX] Thing is, I've got a
set of rules and regulations
I follow to the letter.
I'll take any job for
decent compensation,
but I don't stick my neck
out for free for anyone.
Still, if some wretch is
about to die from hunger,
I'll feed him, at least.
[MAYUKA]
Here.
I can't have you
starving to death
before I manage to get
something out of it.
You must have some
possessions in the city.
[DERRIDA]
No. I don't think I do.
When somebody dies,
what happens to all
their money? Where's it go?
If they have no next of kin,
the government takes it.
So, kid, what the hell
did you do, anyway?
It wasn't me.
It wasn't! I didn't kill Nathan!
I was set up, I swear!
The DZs. They had already been
delivered to the military.
And that snake Andrei,
he tricked us!
And then he came
to silence us!
Relax! I don't even know what
you're babbling on about. Jeez.
--[MAYUKA whimpers]
--Easy.
And my dad... How'd it
end up like this?
[gasps]
[DERRIDA]
The patch file...
If they have it now,
why wasn't the DZ bug fixed?
What if my father hid the key,
and they never got
the patch file?
That'd mean...
[gasps]
Look, I need your help.
I have to find
a girl named Mage.
Can you do me that favor?
I'm not taking another request
until you pay me for today's.
[DERRIDA]
Please! Every moment counts!
[VIDAUX] No. I can't do it
with no chance of compensation.
[DERRIDA]
I have compensation right here!
You wanted to see
the faces of the rats
who made the DZs, didn't you?
Well, I'm one of them.
Derrida Yvain.
Son of Jacques Yvain,
their inventor.
I don't really care what
rich family you came from--
[DERRIDA] I made a patch to
fix a fatal bug in those DZs!
Those Automata going
haywire out there.
Whoever has that patch
can control them all.
That file? It's something
that Rebuild, the army,
and the government must be
falling over each other to find.
But the way things
look out there,
they clearly don't have it yet.
[DERRIDA] They're probably
all desperately looking
for the patch.
[VIDAUX]
And you know where it is?
[DERRIDA] I do, but the file is
set to block unauthorized users
from accessing its data.
So, it can't be opened.
Not without the access key
I left with a girl named Mage.
I'll give the file to you.
You can trade it
with whoever you want.
You'll make a fortune.
And I'll...
Take care... of Mage!
Nathan... I'll find her and
make sure that she's okay.
I made a promise to you,
and I'm going to keep it!
[MAYUKA]
Huh?
--[WOMAN A] Clockwise.
--[WOMAN B] Anti-clockwise.
[VIDAUX]
No information.
[DERRIDA]
Search again, please.
That won't change anything.
And you're sure that her name
is really Mage Bilstein?
I'm positive.
Can you try 'Yuri'?
What's the full name?
I don't know.
Well, then there isn't any
point in running a search.
Fine, just take me to Nathan
Bilstein's house, then.
Nathan had said that he left
Mage with Yuri and her family,
and she always
walked to their house,
so she must live
somewhere nearby.
[MAYUKA] Have you seen
this book before, mister?
[DERRIDA] Yeah. I read
it when I was a kid.
[MAYUKA] Do you think Pinocchio
will become a real boy someday?
Well, uh...
[MAYUKA]
I think he will, for sure!
[DERRIDA]
Oh, I remember.
Yeah, at the end of the story--
[MAYUKA]
Ah! Please, don't tell me!
But...
Instead of reading it, I decided
to make up the ending myself!
That so?
In my ending,
Pinocchio becomes human.
And then a chef!
[giggles]
[DERRIDA]
A chef?
But, he already became
a human like he wanted to,
isn't that enough?
[MAYUKA] Well, not every human
is happy with just being alive.
So, Pinocchio also
gets to be a chef
who makes and eats
all the tasty things
he couldn't have
when he was a puppet!
Doesn't that sound great?
[DERRIDA]
I guess.
[MAYUKA]
I think happiness is getting
to eat lots of delicious things,
whenever you want to.
[DERRIDA]
Oh, no.
[VIDAUX] Looks like it's been
through the wringer.
[VIDAUX]
Move.
--[DERRIDA] Hm?
--[beeping]
[gate clatters]
What are you?
[VIDAUX] I'm a Destruct.
A demolition man.
[gasps, grunts]
Huh?
[DERRIDA]
Mage, is that you?
No way! It's been 10 years.
So, you couldn't be Mage.
[GIRL]
My name is Ange.
[DERRIDA grunts]
What? Ange?
[MAGE]
What song?
[YURI] Here's a hint!
It's one of your favorites!
[music playing on record]
Huh?
[SINGER and YURI]
♪ There is a colorful path ♪
♪ Which has happened ♪
♪ Vividness through
all the motions ♪
What is... this?
♪ Time goes by... ♪
[DERRIDA gasps]
What... happened?
[distant, quiet singing]
[gasps]
[YURI]
♪ ... has happened ♪
♪ Vividness through
all the motions ♪
♪ Colors accentuate identity ♪
♪ Time goes by... ♪
They're dead.
[MAGE]
This way!
When it warms up,
I wanna plant 'em right here!
Mage...
[gun clicks]
[MYSTERY WOMAN]
Stay right there!
Hands up.
Don't turn around,
or I'll shoot!
Who are you?
What'd you come here for?
[gasps]
I know you.
[MYSTERY WOMAN]
Don't move! I will shoot.
'Cept that you can't.
[MYSTERY WOMAN]
What do you mean?
Because that's...
...a camera, isn't it? Yuri.
[gunshot]
[bell rings]
[MARIE]
Your guest has arrived, sir.
Thank you for joining me.
I was just admiring
your skillful display
on the video feed.
Were you?
[ANDREI] Delete the record
of this visitor.
I am seeing no guest here
right now, you understand me?
Now, leave us.
This building has
exceptionally strict security.
The system's perfectly refined.
As you saw, no one
goes unnoticed.
Only those in possession
of an authenticator,
like the one I sent to you,
can get through.
[DONNA] I don't need it.
It's just a nuisance to carry.
Wha--
Don't you know how much
these cost, you imbecilic shrew?
Tell me about the job.
[ANDREI]
I'll pay your fee in advance.
Should you need anything else,
just name it.
And please do feel free
to consider that fancy outfit
a personal present
from me to you,
--if you're so inclined.
--How vile.
I beg your pardon?
[growls]
Fine.
[ANDREI]
This is Derrida Yvain.
He must not be left alive
under any circumstances.
Get rid of him without
anyone finding out.
Quietly. Precisely.
You got that? Donna?
--[gun clicks]
--[gasps]
My pay.
Lily, come here!
Go and fetch the
card from the desk,
and give it to this woman,
then delete this entire
interaction from the record.
Target and reward.
Those are the only
things I require.
[growls]
Damn you!
Who do you think's
in charge here--
[gun clicks
[DONNA]
I will erase him.
[ANDREI gasps]
[doors hiss]
[ANDREI sighs]
[gasps]
That was a warning shot.
[DERRIDA]
Wait! It's me! It's Derrida!
[YURI gasps]
What?
[footsteps]
[YURI]
That can't... Derrida is...
[DERRIDA] Yuri, I was frozen
in cryostasis for 10 years.
[YURI] Oh, sure.
You expect me to believe that?
Listen to me. Where's Mage?
Is she safe somewhere?
Just tell me, please!
I'm sorry.
Mage is dead.
[gasps]
[DERRIDA]
No...
[DONNA]
She can't be...