There's gotta be some way I can
beat Takagi at her own game.
I gotta get that last laugh!
Or, at the very least, I have to do something
to stop her from teasing me every day.
Sorry, I didn't see you...!
Hey, Nishikata.
Good morning.
Oh. Ah. Good morning.
Uh. Something wrong?
Oh, no.
Not at all.
Hmm...
Well, you want to go to school together?
Uh...
Sure.
"Who's Taller?"
Did she see that?
Did she see me apologize to a pole?
Hey, Nishikata.
Yeah? What's up?
Want to tandem ride?
You already know my answer.
We'll get in trouble if we're seen.
You're just too embarrassed.
No, I am not!
Yeah. Right.
Well, she hasn't said anything strange.
Guess she must have just missed seeing me.
Phew.
Took you long enough.
Breaking out the winter uniform?
Yeah. It's been getting colder lately,
so I thought the time was just about right.
Wh-What?
Did you grow?
Huh?
I think that uniform looked a
little bigger on you last spring.
Now that I think about it, she might be right.
This thing feels like it was tailor-made for me.
I didn't even notice.
Could it be?
Am I finally having a growth spurt?
Man.
I'm growing so much lately,
I might need a new uniform soon.
Must be one of those "growth spurts."
But by comparison, you sure haven't
changed much, have you, Takagi?
That's sexual harassment.
"Haven't changed much."
N-No!
That's...
Come on, you know that's not what I was talking about.
Uh. I was talking about your height.
Huh? Well, yeah, I was too.
Why, what did you think I meant?
N-Nothing.
Oh?
Now what?
Hmm...
You know what?
I take it back, maybe you haven't gotten taller.
Huh?!
What do you mean?
I totally grew!
In fact, I'd be willing to bet
I'm taller than you now, Takagi!
Yeah? Do you care to find out for sure?
Why're we doing it here?
So we can take our shoes off to be fair.
We're gonna be late for school.
Nah, this'll be quick.
Here, turn around.
Let's see.
She's kinda... warm.
Uhh...
So, Takagi?
Huh?
Normally, wouldn't you stand against a
wall and make a mark to measure height?
Yeah, but I think it's more accurate
if we stand together like this.
I think we're about the same height.
Huh? Really?
Really.
If you don't believe me, check for yourself.
No way, you're right.
Told yah.
Hey.
You're not like, on your tiptoes are you?
Why? You don't trust me?
All right then.
Is this better?
You'll be able to tell if I'm cheating now.
Uh. Yeah. I guess.
Wait.
Now it kinda looks like.
I'm taller.
That's because I was on my tiptoes before.
So you were cheating, I
called it! You're a liar!
I never said I wasn't on my tiptoes.
Good for you though.
You're taller after all.
Yeah, walk away.
You're acting all cool on the outside,
but on the inside, I bet you're really bitter!
Oh. By the way,
if you think I'm bitter, you're wrong.
Know why?
When your body grows too fast.
You might run into things.
Like, utility poles.
Huh?
Wait! Does that mean you saw me do that?
Are you ready?
School's a-waiting'!
Takagi.
Hey.
Takagi?
So cold.
I dunno, I feel fine.
You're so sensitive to the cold, Yukari.
Take that!
Mina, your hand is freezing!
"I Hate the Cold"
Jeez.
You do that again, and I'll hate you forever.
Forever?
Will you stop it?
Why?
Because I hate it!
Why are your hands so cold anyway?
You know why.
You just don't want to accept it.
People who have cold hands have warm hearts!
I don't think a person with a warm heart
would enjoy torturing their friends for kicks.
Now, now.
There's no need to hold a grudge.
I'm not kidding. If you do it
again, I'm gonna be really mad.
You're already mad.
Gotcha.
So cold!
Stop it!
I said stop, Sanae!
That's the "My heart is so warm" attack.
Help me, Yukari!
Take this!
Now let's see how you like it!
Your hands are so warm. It's scary.
That must mean you've got a cold heart.
That is not what it means and you know it!
Stay away, cold-heart!
Prepare for the "Cold heart frozen soul" attack!
Equally as fearsome!
It's not even close!
Hey.
So cold!
What'd you do that for?
Get me back if you can.
You get back here!
Stop that!
Quadruple cold hands!
Four times the power!
No way can I do that.
Will you stop it?! Your hands
are cold as ice! Leave me alone!
Did you know they say that people
with cold hands have warm hearts?
Nope!
It's Takagi and Nishikata, again.
I saw them show up to school together today.
Those two are so close.
Well, maybe they are going out.
"Invitation"
I really can't help but wonder.
Do you think they're going out?
Who knows?
You don't sound very interested.
They're so close, it makes me want to know.
Why is that?
Are you jealous of them?
Am I jealous?
Well, not exactly, but...
Mina.
Yukari says she wishes she had
a boy she could flirt with.
That's not even close to what I said!
Hey.
You listening?
Mina?
Sanae! I'm on the toilet.
Don't talk to me right now, please!
You're gonna make me lose my concentration!
Huh?
You are too much sometimes, Sanae.
It's good.
You should watch it later.
Really? Cool, I will!
Hey, Takagi?
Hmm?
I just came up with the perfect plan!
It's the ultimate, fail-proof plot to
tease Takagi on our way home from school!
Hmm?
What are you smirking to yourself about over there?
Something pervy?
No.
It's nothing dirty or weird or whatever.
Dirty or weird?
That's what I said!
Your face is turning red.
Whatever.
Just you wait until after school!
By the way, Nishikata.
Later, do you wanna walk home together?
Yeah, sure!
Oh, no!
Was I too eager?
Did she realize I'm up to something?
I mean.
Yeah, sure.
Isn't that what you just said?
Uh-huh.
That a problem?
Hmm...
No.
But just in case you change
your mind before school's out,
you can give me a definite answer later.
See ya.
Well that was weird.
As long as she isn't on to me, I guess it's fine.
Hey, Nishikata!
We were gonna play "Super-Pro" at my house today.
You want in on that?
Um...
Sorry. I can't today.
You spending time with your girlfriend again?
My "girlfriend"?
Takagi, right? I called it.
Huh?! What are you talking about?
We're not like that at all!
It's true, Takagi and Nishikata are not going out.
I know 'cuz we just asked her in the bathroom.
Aw, really?
Yeah!
Oh man, I seriously gotta go.
Bathroom, here I come.
Uhh... What was she doing in the
bathroom before if she has to go now?
All right, putting that aside,
if you're not going out with her,
why are you walking home with
her for like the hundredth time?
Well, because she asked me to?
Asked you?
And you're sure that's not because you're going out?
Uh.
I don't think so, at least.
Hmm?
Okay, whatever.
Hey, isn't next period in the lab?
You're right, let's hurry!
No way.
I don't buy it.
Takagi just wants to tease me.
Ready to get going?
Yeah. But we're going straight home today, okay?
Huh?!
But I had it all planned out!
I wanted to get a Ponkan Popsicle!
Don't you think it's a little bit cold for that?
Not when you go inside and pump the heat it's not!
You said it.
If she's not gonna say anything about it,
then to give her my "definite"
answer, I've gotta ask her myself.
That's kinda embarrassing now
that I'm face to face with it.
I've never been the one to ask
her to walk home with me before.
Nishikata.
Yeah? What's going' on?
Oh, good!
If she asks me, all I have to do is say yes!
That's easy!
You know what?
Earlier today someone asked me
if I was going out with you.
Huh?!
And...
After I told them we weren't,
they said that they thought I liked you.
I'm always asking you to walk home with me.
Maybe that's why they thought that.
I should have known!
This is what you were after the whole time!
Hmm?
You orchestrated everything, so I have no
choice but to ask you to walk home with me!
Just so you can watch me squirm!
You okay?
Try to sound calm.
Just say something like, "Oh yeah? That's funny."
Oh yeah? Tha-That's funny!
Nice!
Uh.
So, anyway.
About your request from this morning.
Hmm?
Uh.
I don't have any plans, so uh...
Let's...
"Let's" what?
Hang in there, man!
If you can get through this,
then you get your chance to mess with Takagi!
Let's walk home together.
I'll have to think about it.
Huh?!
I'm just kidding.
Let's go.
I can't wait.
Because... it looks like you're scheming something.
She's on to me!
If she's already suspicious of
me, should I hold off on my plan?
But I came up with such a good idea!
Not that I've thought about how to carry
out said idea to begin with, though.
Want to get some juice?
Now that I think about it, my mouth is dry.
Aww.
Most of them are sold out.
I really wanted to get something cold.
But all they have is...
Sweet red bean soup and whatever that is!
What do we do?
I need something, but I'm
in a no-win situation here!
A "no-win situation"?
Should we find another vending machine?
Nah.
I'm thirsty, so I guess...
...I'll just go for this one.
Gross.
With a name like that, duh.
On any other day,
I'd completely regret buying this.
But now I know for sure that my new plan will work!
Hey, Takagi.
Hmm?
Say there's one juice that's
really tasty but gives you a fever.
And another that's just plain disgusting.
Which would you choose?
Hmm...
"Two-Choice Question"
One juice that's really tasty but gives you a fever
and another that's just plain disgusting?
Hmm...
How's it feel?
You can't decide, can you?
Feel the unease!
I want to see your face contorted
with conflicting emotions!
'Kay, question.
So if I drank the tasty juice and got a fever.
Would you come and visit me while I'm stuck at home?
What?
What's the point in asking me that?
Does it affect your answer?
Significantly.
You wouldn't visit, then?
Uh.
Hey. I didn't say that. Don't put words in my mouth.
If you were out sick, then I'd visit you.
Then I'd take the tasty one.
Well, this is weird.
What's going on?
I expected her to be conflicted, but
she doesn't have a care in the world.
Hold on.
I feel a little weird now.
Am I the loser here?
Has my "two-choice question" plan failed?
No, it's still too early to give up!
'Kay!
Next question!
Okay.
No more allowance for your whole life,
or no more teasing me ever?!
No allowance for life.
So quick!
I'd be fine.
I've been saving up my New Year's money
and anything else I've gotten for a while.
And once I'm in high school, I'd just get a job.
Clearly, the better choice is to keep teasing you.
I underestimated her!
I'll need a better question than that.
Nishikata.
What?
Well, you've asked me two weird questions in a row.
What's your angle?
Are you just trying to give me a hard time?
Huh?
Not really.
Fine.
Then I'll ask you one, now.
Would you rather that I disappear
or that you'd have to be teased by me forever?
What'll you choose?
Huh?
What do you mean "disappear?"
Poof, I'm gone.
I don't want to be teased for the
rest of my life but for her to disappear?
That feels like a step too far.
I'd, uh, choose to be teased.
Thought so.
You do like being teased.
No, I don't!
Why would anyone like that?
It's just...
I don't exactly want you to disappear either.
That would suck.
You want to be with me?
That it?
That's not...
Made you blush!
Man, why does she always have to do this?
Is it that fun to see me uncomfortable?
I gotta come up with a good question to get back at her.
Question two.
Huh? You're not done?
You get zeroes on all tests for the rest of your life,
or you have kiss me.
Which is it?
A "kiss"?!
Gotta choose one.
I'd get a zero even if I study well?
Yep.
It doesn't matter what you do.
I couldn't live with that!
My parents would take away my allowance immediately,
and there's no way I'd get into high school!
But if choose the kiss,
she's gonna make fun of me like there's no tomorrow!
Hard decision, huh?
Man!
The more I struggle to choose, the happier she gets!
I gotta choose quickly.
All zeroes for life is too much!
But!
I have no choice!
I'll pick not getting zeroes on my tests.
Sorry, which option was that again?
Th-The one with the kiss.
Ho, ho?
Is that so?
Okay, then.
Aww, man.
Looks like you were right.
You are taller than me.
What's with that look?
I was just making sure.
She's messed with me so many times today.
But I have this all figured out now.
One option has to be something she'd never choose,
and the other just has to be something
I can make fun of her for picking!
That way, I win no matter what!
Okay, Takagi. I got one...
All right, next question.
You have to go around the school while
doing a handstand, or you and I...
Whoa, hold on a second! I can't even do
a hand stand, that option doesn't work!
And when can I ask the questions again?
As soon as you're done answering my questions.
What? Why?