Sanae!
Here! For you.
Uh... A love letter?
Of course not! It's just a regular letter!
Everyone's writing them to their
friends these days! Haven't you noticed?
No.
Don't you worry, Yukari, I'm gonna write one for you too.
That's nice of you, just don't do it in class.
You need to focus on the lesson.
Friendship is way more important than any lesson.
What, are the girls all suddenly into writing letters now?
That's what it looks like.
I wonder if some of them are writing love letters, too.
Maybe. They do seem really into it.
I'll say.
Love letters, huh?
I don't get the appeal.
They could just say what they want out
loud. Why bother to write it all down?
Must have a lotta time on their hands.
I'm sorry! I'm sorry! I'm sorry! I'm sorry!
Sanae, you're going a little overboard.
One kick was enough.
So kicking him at all's okay?
All right, let's start class.
Open up your textbooks to page seventy-six.
Takagi's writing letters, too?
Sometimes I forget that she's just your ordinary girl.
What?
"Letter"
Is there something wrong, Nishikata?
No, nothing, everything's great!
A letter? Who's it from?
And why me?
I wonder if some of them are writing love letters, too.
No, no, no, that's obviously not it!
Someone's playing a prank on me.
Oh, yeah!
This could be Takagi's doing.
No, it's gotta be her!
Takagi...
Wait a second.
Reign it in, Nishikata!
What if it's somebody else? What if it isn't Takagi?
If she finds out I got a letter,
she'll just use that to tease me again!
Yeah? What is it?
Uh...
Oh, uh...
I was just thinking.
It's nice out.
Are you hiding something?
Why would I be hiding something?
Hmm...
Dunno. But you're suspicious.
And blushing, too.
You're just imagining things.
Well, maybe.
But why is your textbook closed?
Well. You see, I uh...
I bet it's why your face is red.
No, it's not! And my face is not red!
Are you sure nothing's wrong?
Yes, that's why I said so!
I guess I was imagining things.
By the way, that letter in your textbook.
I put that there.
I knew it!
Yeah. I knew that.
I mean, duh. It was obvious.
You liar.
What are you talking about? I'm not lying.
I was just having fun making you squirm.
So. You gonna read what's inside?
You wrote something?
Well, it is a letter.
You're just messing with me like always, aren't you?
Why aren't you saying something?
Okay.
I'll read it at home later.
Read it now.
What? Why now?
Because. School's over after this period.
And I wanted an answer by then.
An answer?
If it's a letter that needs an answer,
then it's a letter asking a question.
Does that mean it's not just meant to mess with me?
I wonder if some of them are writing love letters, too.
What if Takao's right?
What if it's a love letter?
Is that even possible?
By any chance, would this
happen to be a love letter, or...?
What's with the silence?!
Why don't you just read it?
Uh, I will, just gimme a minute.
I gotta open it up first.
Based on that reaction, I'd wager anything
that this is designed just to tease me.
Whatever it ends up saying, I have to be firm
and confident so that she doesn't get the chance.
Be bold! Be brave!
But what if...
No, it can't be.
Why would it be?
There's no way!
But if it is a love letter, then... I...
You could have just asked me to my face.
But everyone's writing letters now. It's cool.
However, I was also curious how you'd react.
So I was right! You were messing with me!
Shut it, Nishikata!
"First Day of School"
Thanks a lot.
I appreciate it, young man.
Welcome. I gotta go now.
Oh, one second!
What's your name, new kid?
Did I forget to say?
I'm Nishikata.
Nishikata. Congrats on getting in!
Mm-hmm.
Thanks.
You'll all be learning alongside each
other over the course of the next year.
I'm not gonna force you to get along with everybody.
But I hope you realize you're only gonna
make the experience worse if you don't.
Oh, no, did I lose it somewhere?
Well, I don't want to bore you right
off the bat with a long speech, so...
Slept in on the first day?
No, I was, uh...
If nothing else, I admire your audacity.
But... Sir, I...
What's your name?
It's Nishikata.
All right, then. Sit down.
Uh... Yes, sir.
Oh, great, Everyone's staring.
I have to make friends with people and clear things up
before I become known as "that
guy who was late on day one."
Mr. Tanabe, a moment of your time?
They called and said they're running a little bit late.
Really?
Are we pushing the entrance ceremony back?
Yes, I'll keep you posted.
I just got word that the entrance
ceremony is running behind schedule.
Sounds like it's gonna take a
while before they're all set up.
So in the meantime...
...we're figuring out seating.
At least I'm not in the front. Sucks to be you.
Oh, come on.
I'm literally as far in the corner as I possibly can be.
Normally I'd be happy about being
this far away from the teacher.
It's the best spot to goof off.
But I don't know anyone as it is!
There's no one behind me or to my left.
Worse, I'm sitting next to a girl.
Did you actually sleep in?
She's talking to me.
It looked like you were about
to say something to the teacher.
Uh... Yeah.
No. I didn't actually sleep in.
If only I'd made it here earlier.
I was at the school on time, but...
It's Takagi's fault.
Whoever that is.
Huh?
All right everyone, head to the gym.
Let's keep quiet.
And no running
Okay.
Hey!
You want to walk there together?
Sure.
Wait a second.
You will soon be given a great gift, the right to vote.
With it, you will choose students
for positions of responsibility.
It's important you select politicians
who are worthy of your trust and confidence.
Similarly, your mothers and fathers
choose their representatives by voting...
Wasn't that speech crazy long?
That dude was talking so long I almost fell asleep!
I know, it was like when we started elementary school.
You're pretty cool for coming' in late on the first day.
I didn't mean to.
Everybody quit yapping' and take your seats.
I'm sorry for getting back late, sir.
Just go sit down.
That's it for today, but remember,
real classes start tomorrow.
Don't mess around because I'm letting you out early.
Go straight home.
Hey, Nishikata.
How 'bout I try to guess why you were late today?
I bet I can.
If I get it right on my first try, I win.
Sure, I guess.
Wait, how is she gonna figure it out on her first try?
You were delivering a lost item.
What? How'd you know?
Hey. Quiet down, Nishikata.
I'm sorry, sir.
How did you know?
How indeed.
Uh... Wait.
You're Takagi?
You weren't here yet when everyone introduced themselves.
What's with that reaction?
Hey! I just said to be quiet!
Sorry!
Thanks a lot. For picking it up.
It's nice to meet you.
It's nice to meet you, too.
"Seating Arrangement"
Seventy-two! Seventy-three!
Seventy-four! Seventy-five!
All this work's finally starting' to pay off!
Oh, man.
She's not here yet.
Morning, Nishikata.
Oh, good morning yourself, Takagi!
So, hey. Have you heard?
They're going to be changing where everyone sits today.
Really? When?
During homeroom.
Homeroom? That's first period!
Taka...
Are you okay?
First period, huh?
That'll be kinda fun.
Yeah?
Well, I mean, we haven't had a
seating change in a while, so...
Yeah, sure.
I guess there are always positives.
But if I'm being honest.
I wanted to be next to you for a while longer.
She's just messing with me again.
I almost fell for it.
Does anyone still need a number? No?
Then move your desks according to the layout on the board.
What number did you draw?
Twenty-nine.
Oh. The far back again, then.
What about you?
This time I'm front and center.
Oh.
We're going to be pretty far.
Yeah.
Later.
All right! Now you can sneak me answers on all our tests!
What? That's cheating.
I'm not doing that.
It's called mutual aid.
Oh, yeah?
Well what do I get out of it?
Words of encouragement from your friend!
Yay...
Yo, Nishikata.
Are you sitting' here?
Nah, over there.
Oh, yeah?
That's too bad. I was hoping we'd be closer.
Yeah, me too.
My vision's been getting really bad lately.
I hope I can see what's on the board.
Oh. So that's it.
I'm next to Nishikata, huh?
You okay, Mano?
Yeah. I'm just great.
What's up? Are you not happy?
It's nothing. Feel free to just ignore me.
I'm just depressed because I'm not sitting near Nakai.
I was really hoping we'd be next to each other.
How far away is he?
Hey.
Someone!
Anyone! Please switch seats with me!
How am I supposed to sneak an early
lunch if I'm right in front of the teacher?
You aren't switching seats
unless you have a legitimate reason.
Also, Kimura.
Please, do see me after class.
Right in front of the teacher?
But if I'm being honest. I wanted
to be next to you for a while longer.
Hey, Kimura, listen!
I can't see the board from here; let's switch!
Oh. Thanks!
But I already found someone.
It's not like I care.
Nishikata. Hey.
What the...?
Guess what? I'm sitting here now.
Wha...? But how?
Well, first Nakai and Kimura switched.
Because Nakai couldn't see the board well enough.
So Nakai was all the way up front.
When she saw that, Mano wanted to switch
with me, since I was right next to him.
Mano's short, so she prefers the front anyway.
Oh. I see.
Nishikata.
You tried to sit next to me up there, didn't you?
No, I...
I couldn't see the board well from here.
Hmm?
Oh, yeah?
Mmm?
What? It's true!
All right, we're starting class.
Get your textbooks out.
Oh. That reminds me.
What was it that you wanted to say earlier today?
What, did I read you wrong?
I thought you were looking for an opportunity.
Sorry.
It took me a while to return this.
Thank you.
From over summer break?
Uh... Yeah.
From then, and...
The first day of school?
You remembered that?
Of course I did. You did too.
Heh! Thank you.
I made sure to wash it for you.
Oh, nothing.
I'm just kinda glad.
Why?
Oh. Y'know...
For a lot.
That I got to return your handkerchief.
And that we ended up next to each other again, oh!
And also...
Well, yeah.
I'm looking forward to this.
So here, we'd say, "I do not agree."
Or you could contract it to, "I don't agree."
That part's pretty easy.
But on the next page, things
get a little more complicated.