"Coffee"
Ugh. Bitter.
What's going' on with your face?
Ugh.
Huh? Wait. Isn't that coffee?
I thought you hated the stuff, Mina.
Why would you buy it you hate it?
Well, I'm becoming more of an adult now, so I
thought I should try to get myself used to it.
Huh?
How exactly are you more of adult now?
Ah! Hey, I may not be tall, but I'm growing in some ways!
I'd like to see you drink this, Sanae!
No problem.
I like it black.
Huh?
You like it black?
Do you wanna trade with me, then?
I do. But I'm an adult, so...
Three, two, one...
Okay, whatever, let's trade!
Yes!
Ahhh... So good.
You sure you're okay with this?
Yeah.
There's gotta be some adults who can't drink coffee.
You know you're a kid right?
Why're you so mean?
Ahh!
Ahhh! Ow!
Oh great.
Adults don't try to tackle their friends, Mina.
As I've come to expect, Takagi made fun of me a ton today.
But I'll get her tomorrow!
Nishikata.
Takagi!
Oh.
On your own today?
Yeah.
Cool. Let's walk home together.
Uh. Wait, why?
What?
Um, sorry.
I thought I heard something.
But, um, you're on your bike, and all.
I'll just push.
"Empty Can"
That's that new drink that just came out, isn't it?
Is it good?
What is this?
Some kind of trap?
I like it.
You wanna have a sip?
Can I?
Mm-hmm.
Great. Thank you.
Not that I really mind,
but won't it be like we're
indirectly kissing or something?
How's that, Takagi? Super embarrassing, right?
You're so embarrassed!
Wha...? How?
She's not embarrassed in the slightest!
What is with her?
Ahh...
Boy, that was good.
Thanks again.
Can't drink it?
No. Of course I can drink it.
It's nothing.
No big deal.
It's like an indirect kiss.
Aah!
You're so jumpy.
There's gotta be a trash can around here.
Man!
Wow!
That was a pretty good shot, Nishikata.
I just threw it without thinking.
I didn't expect to make it in.
This is crazy!
I didn't know I was such a good shot!
All right.
I wanna give this a go.
What are you aiming at?
You weren't even close!
You're terrible at this!
Oh? Care to make it interesting?
Yeah, fine.
I can't say "no" when winning's a sure-thing.
Then, we'll each throw one can at a time.
The first person to make it in, wins.
Challenging me to a match she can't possibly win.
Takagi's really lost her cool this time.
And it feels awesome!
So if you somehow win,
then I guess I'll do anything you want me to.
I'm gonna hold you to that.
You better not chicken out later.
No way.
Besides, it's not like I'm gonna lose to you.
Glad to hear it.
If you miss, that means I win.
Ugh.
She totally tricked me again.
Just stand at the same place and use the same angle.
Okay.
I can do this.
It's a walk in the park!
Oh, yeah.
So, uh, if you happen to win,
then I'll let you have my first kiss.
Looks like I win!
That wasn't fair.
What wasn't?
Whaddya mean "what wasn't"? As I threw it, you said...
Hmm? Said what?
Oh, forget it.
Okay.
Well, a promise is a promise.
Now what should I make you do?
I don't even want to think about what she might say.
Know what?
How about this?
You can do whatever.
Wait, where are you going Takagi?!
Don't pity me! I need consequences!
Letting me off like this makes me feel
like I'll never beat you at anything.
You never will beat me at anything.
Huh? What's that supposed to mean?
Hey!
"Soda"
Ahh!
So fizzy.
What is it this time?
Huh? You're drinking soda?
I thought you didn't like soda, though.
Why do sodas have to be so fizzy? It stings!
Is there a reason you keep
buying drinks you don't even like?
Pretending to be an adult again?
No, not that.
I just love the flavor.
But it stings bad!
My poor tongue is hurting so bad!
You're so annoying.
What?
Don't act like it doesn't hurt
your tongue when you have this stuff!
It doesn't.
Prove it. Have some right now.
All right.
Ahh!
The pain'll bubble up inside you soon.
Yeah, not likely.
Tell the truth. You're feeling it, aren't you?
No, I'm not.
Hmm...
What pain is she talking about? I'm fine.
Oh no.
I'm about to burp.
Ha! You feeling' it now?
Nuh-uh.
If I burp right now, she's gonna make fun of me.
But this stupid fizz is still coming up.
I can't hold it much longer!
Agh! It's so tingly, I hate it!
Ahhh...
What's your problem?
Nothing.
Why am I still drinking this?
See you tomorrow!
Just you wait, Takagi.
Including the walk home, she
teased me 15 times in total today.
Each time I make a mistake
during a game, I make a note of it.
Then I train ten times harder for each one.
I believe that will lead me to my next victory.
That's it!
Today I had 15 losses.
And that times ten is 150!
Uh... That might be too much for my first go.
Okay.
Let's try three times first.
One, two, three.
Eighteen.
Nineteen.
This is a lot harder than I thought!
Maybe I shouldn't do so many.
No, I have to!
This is my punishment for letting
Takagi mess with me so many times!
I'll savor this agony and use it as
motivation to get back at her next time!
I can do this!
"Muscle Training"
What's wrong?
Is your arm hurt?
Pull a muscle?
Huh? Oh, no, it's nothing like
that. It's just extra sore is all.
Huh?
I just said it was sore! That really hurts!
Does that count as her first teasing of the day?
I should probably be holding myself accountable.
So I guess that's one.
Hey!
That was way too easy!
You must be really sore if flinching hurts.
Okay, well that was definitely teasing, no doubt about it.
So... wanna tell me why you're sore all of a sudden?
Uhh. I started to work out yesterday, so you know.
Interesting.
I hope you don't quit after like, three days.
Hah. Go ahead.
Laugh it up now.
Why?
She teased me 23 times today! Is that a record?
Either way, it's much more than yesterday!
One, two, three.
Hey, whatever happened to working out, Nishikata?
Nothing, I still do it daily.
Oh wow.
So you didn't quit three days in?
Yes, thanks to you.
Oh! But you know what I heard?
Huh? No, what?
They say if you work out too much during your
growth spurt, it'll stop you from getting taller.
Uh, wait?
Huh?! Oh no!
I think I did hear that somewhere before!
That's not good!
If she ends ups taller than me because I'm
stunting my own growth, I'll never heard the end of it!
She'll make fun of me forever!
What do I do, what do I do?
But that is just a rumor.
Just a rumor?
In fact, I've also heard moderate
exercise actually supports your growth.
So, that being the case, you should keep working out.
Nothing to worry about.
It's a good idea.
And to be honest,
you kinda look a bit more muscular.
You think?
What's wrong?
You're quiet.
Don't tell me that you're blushing.
I'm not blushing.
But your face is red.
Yeah, you're definitely blushing all right.
Why do you always have to tease me every single day?
Because I like seeing your reactions, duh.
By the way,
I wasn't lying when I said you look muscular.
Honestly, you've looked pretty good lately.
You're even redder now!
Whatever! It's just because it's hot outside!
Hey!
Takagi!
Come back!
The count is 54 today.
Oh, 55 including this last one.
But I'm starting to think that I should keep
working out even if Takagi doesn't tease me.
“Dubbing”
Chester dear, are you eating dinner at home tonight?
Well, I reckon' that depends on work.
If we go too late, I'll just
eat with Jirou on my way home.
I'm glad you've found a close friend in Jirou,
but you should have dinner at home sometimes.
It's starting to feel lonely without you.
Yeah, but it's mah job, what can yah do?
Can we please just go home?
No way! We're having' fun!
Why are you still talking like that?
So annoying.
Uh...
You jerk!
Am I really so unimportant to you?
Aww, Pudding', don't be like that.
I'm doing' mah best here.
Why are you crying' mah darling'?
Well, it's as if Jirou and your
work have taken you away from me.
I just...
I don't think I can take it any longer.
Emotions are running high.
Ahh jeez, I'm sick o' this!
How could you say such a thing, Chester? Oh!
Listen here.
If yer gonna act like this.
Then so will I!
Uh... Hold on.
Did you realize those cats are both male?
Hey, whaddya know, it's Chester!
Well, if it ain't Jirou!
Wanna grab a bite to eat?
I really want to go home.
"Umbrella"
Aww! Of course it starts raining right when school ends.
Huh?! No one told me it was gonna rain today!
If I knew, I would have brought my raincoat!
Dummy.
Hey, don't be so mean to Mina.
You want to take the bus home, then?
I don't have any bus money either.
See what I mean, dumb.
Oh, you be quiet.
I'll lend you some cash, don't worry.
Man.
I got teased a ton today, too.
Huh? Aren't you heading home, Takagi?
Not yet.
I didn't bring a raincoat or an umbrella.
You are such an airhead!
You really didn't know it was gonna rain today?
How ditzy can you be?
No comeback?
Oh.
Come to think of it, your umbrella is pretty big, right?
Huh?
We look like a couple under this umbrella together.
How in the world did this happen?
I feel so weird!
It's super awkward!
What should I do?
Fill the silence, I guess.
So, uh, what about your bike?
It's still at school, but I'll walk tomorrow.
Oh. Okay.
It's even more awkward now that I tried to fill
the silence, and it worked for all of five seconds!
Ugh. I'm so embarrassed that it's getting hard to breathe.
I need to distract myself somehow.
Hey, Takagi!
How's this?
Are you scared?
Surprised?
Give me something!
Aww. He's so cute!
Excuse me?
Ugh, what was I thinking?
This is Takagi I'm dealing with, of course she's fine!
Wait, what?
Don't freak, it's just a frog.
By the way, Nishikata.
Is your shoulder getting wet over there?
Yeah, sort of.
It's not that bad, though.
Getting wet at all can lead to a cold.
I'm gonna scoot closer, so get
yourself all the way under the umbrella.
My heart's pounding so fast.
It feels like it's about to burst!
Calm down, calm down, Nishikata!
If she finds out you're nervous,
she's gonna make fun of you again!
Just talk about something.
Anything!
So hey, uh...
Hmm?
It's pretty unusual for you to forget
your umbrella when it's supposed to rain.
Could it be that you really are an
airhead, and I was right all along?
Was that too harsh?
Hmmm...
Yeah, maybe.
I do tend to be sort of forgetful.
Did I hear that right?
Did she just admit she has a fault?
What a rare occasion!
I feel like I've won for once!
I'm having trouble remembering
something right now, actually.
Oh, yeah?
Do you need help?
Mm-hmm.
The two of us, all close, sharing the same umbrella.
We must look like a...
What was the word for it?
I just can't seem to remember it.
Uhh.
Wait, you don't mean...
It's on the tip of my tongue!
Uh... We look like a couple?
Huh? What was that?
I didn't quite hear you.
Oh, I remember!
It was "couple"!
Come on, there's no way you forgot that!
Oh, what about that thing that couples do?
You know.
It's a way they express their love.
When they take their lips and then
press them up against each other?
If I don't answer her, then I lose!
A... A kiss?
Huh? I can't hear you, the rain's too loud.
What do you mean?
It's not raining that hard anymore.
Hmm?
So don't pretend you didn't hear me.
I said it's a kiss.
Ahh. That was it.
So how about that phrase they
always use to show their feelings?
Know that?
You know.
That one.
Not I "like" you, but...
Pretty sure it starts out the same.
"I" something.
Uh, I dunno.
I think the next word starts with "L" too.
I said I don't know!
Nah, you know this one.
"I"...
The next word starts with "L-O."
"I lo"... What's the next letter?
You know it.
Th-That's enough.
Oh! The last word is "you."
You're not gonna let up, are you?
Ugh, man!
Hey, check it out, the rain stopped!
Yeah, you're right.
I'm saved!
There was no way I could survive that
treatment until we reached her house!
Well, my place is this way.
Now that the skies are clear, I'll be going.
Where are we?
I don't know how to get home from here.
Ugh!
Will you ever give me a break?