Well...
As I'm sure you know, summer vacation starts
tomorrow. Try not to get into any trouble.
Summer vacation is gonna be awesome!
Hey.
We're thinking of going to the beach tomorrow, you in?
Yeah, you know it, dude.
I suddenly have a huge craving for watermelon!
I'd eat some watermelon.
Perfect! Let's get one for tomorrow!
Good idea!
"Tandem Riding"
Summer vacation.
You excited?
Yeah.
It feels like I've been waiting for it forever.
Now I can play as much as I want!
I'm a free man!
You better not forget about your homework.
Knowing you, you'll put it off.
I bet you're thinking "play first, work later."
How'd you know?
Haha! So I was right?
Well yeah.
But the whole point of a break is to relax, right?
I wanna go to the pool, hit the
beach, and go camping and stuff.
Man, I barely have enough time to do all that!
I wish we could just have summer vacation forever.
Yeah?
I like going to school, too, though.
Because...
It's fun.
No more of that for a while, huh?
So hot!
But the breeze feels great!
Can you go faster? This rocks!
You wouldn't be saying that if you were pedaling!
It's hot out.
Should we do what they were doing?
Huh?!
Of course, you'd have to be in the front.
No. We can't!
Uh. 'Cuz it'd be dangerous with cars driving by, you know?
There are no cars around.
It's not even a public road.
Yeah, but.
Hold on.
Are you embarrassed or something?
No! Of course I'm not embarrassed!
Oh.
You can't do it, then?
What are you talking about?
Tandem riding is super easy.
I just don't think we should do it, 'cuz it's not safe.
Let's go to the vacant lot, then.
Huh?!
If you can't do it, then you owe me a juice.
I hope you're not too thirsty,
because I got this, no sweat.
Hmm?
That was just the practice run!
I can do this!
I'll take grape.
Could ya gimme a second?!
Is it really this hard to ride with
someone sitting on the back of a bike?
Just checking, but you're not trying to
throw us off balance on purpose, are you?
Of course not.
Are you sure.
I'm just sitting how I usually sit.
If we can't get it to work, then it's gotta be your fault.
I mean...
...the last time I did this with someone.
They didn't have any trouble peddling.
Oh, really?
That's cool.
I take it they were a girl?
Nope.
Not a girl.
I see.
One more time.
I think I've almost got it!
This time for sure!
What's going on?
Why do I feel so frustrated?
I'm just riding a bike!
What's up?
You're getting into this.
I'm not!
I just don't wanna waste my hard earned money on you!
Yeah, that's it!
I just don't want to buy her a drink! That's all!
Hey!
We're moving!
By the way, Nishikata,
the last time I rode on the back of someone's bike,
it was my dad's.
I think I was four at the time.
Take it.
Why, thank you.
Ahh...
That's good!
Are you not gonna get yourself a drink, too?
Uh. Nope.
I'm, uhh, not thirsty.
I can't tell her I have no money to buy my own.
How would that look?
Want some?
No.
I'm fine, thanks.
She'd just call it an indirect
kiss again to get me to blush.
Come on, I know you're thirsty.
Have some.
I really don't want any.
Endure it.
You can do it.
Endure.
Drink this.
We can't have you getting heatstroke.
I can have it?
Yeah.
Besides.
I know you.
You don't want mine because it's an indirect kiss.
Huh?!
Tha-That's not it!
I'm just not thirsty!
Right.
But you'll drink yours?
Well, you already bought it.
It'd be a waste when it's this hot.
Thanks for the drink.
We won't be walking home from school for a while.
Ahhh...
Got that right.
We're on vacation, after all.
I know!
How about starting tomorrow, we
practice tandem riding here until noon?
Okay, I guess.
But not on the road.
That's what I meant.
We'll just ride here.
If we're only ever gonna ride
here, there's no point in practicing.
Yeah, there is.
You know.
Summer vacation.
It starts tomorrow.
What does that mean?
All right!
Well, we should head home.
Summer vacation.
Huh?
I'm excited.
It'll be fun!
Yeah, obviously.
"First Day of Summer Vacation"
Why'd it have to rain on our first day off?
I know.
Summer vacation's barely even
started, and my plans are already ruined!
It's not like it's supposed to rain tomorrow.
I wanted to go to the pool today.
And I'm never getting that time back!
Please stop crying.
You know we can't do anything about the rain.
Let's just start our homework.
Huh?
What's with those faces?
Don't tell me you two didn't bring yours.
I told you guys to bring your
homework over since it's raining out!
I figured I must have misheard you.
Unbelievable!
Why do we get assigned homework during
summer vacation in the first place?
It's a violation of human rights.
It's hardly a break with homework.
Right?
Dream all you want, we still have to do it.
Ugh! Do me a personal favor, Yukari
quit doing your homework and relax!
Seeing you do yours reminds me that I
have to do mine, and now I can't enjoy myself!
Whatever!
Maybe you need the reminder!
It's only the first day still.
Just forget about school.
Typical, from a person who will be
crying with regret on August thirty-first.
You're so stubborn.
Forget you. I'm gonna read manga.
Yeah?
Fine.
Hey, Yukari?
Hmm?
I got a great idea. Can we write our book report on manga?
Yes, please.
Can you two just go home already?
"Test of Courage"
It stopped raining.
Awesome!
Wait, why exactly am I happy about that again?
Nishikata.
You're here.
Yeah, we made a promise, didn't we?
Guess so.
Something wrong?
Uh.
No.
It's nothing.
Whoa.
There are so many puddles here.
Well, you know what they say.
When it rains, it pours.
I didn't recognize her for a second there.
Come to think of it, I've run into her
a few times on our days off by chance,
but this is our first time meeting up.
No way!
This isn't like, a date, is it?
No, obviously not!
We're just here to practice
tandem riding, like we agreed to!
Nishikata?
Huh?! What's up?
You hear me?
Hello?
No. Sorry.
What did you say?
This place is in pretty bad riding condition.
Uh, yeah.
Actually,
I was planning to go out after we practiced today.
No sense going back home.
Do you wanna hang out with me to kill some time?
Okay.
Is this a date?
No, no, no.
No way!
Uh. Yeah, that's fine.
But let's go someplace where there aren't too many people.
There's no telling what our
classmates would say if they saw us!
Hmmm...
How about...
That's it!
A test of courage?
Perfect for summer, right?
Wouldn't it be scarier if we did it at night?
Not by much.
I heard it gets pitch black when you're in there.
Some say, there's a presence.
Sorry.
What?
A presence?
Well, that's what I heard.
This tunnel doesn't have any sharp turns.
But for some reason, a lot of cars
ended up crashing straight into the walls.
So they had to make a new road nearby.
And since then, every night, without
fail, a bloodthirsty ghost appears.
Looking for cars to prey upon.
But there's even more to it.
Rumor has it.
People are spirited away here.
Dozens.
Maybe more have disappeared right in this very tunnel.
Are you going in?
Or are you chicken?
I am so not chicken!
It's the middle of the day!
Why would I be scared of going
in some dusty, stupid, old tunnel?
It's way darker than I thought.
Why is the wind making such a weird noise?
Hey.
Check out what's on the wall.
A talisman?
For spirits.
It keeps them away.
So clearly,
there must be something evil in here.
I'm not surprised you're scared.
I'm not! I was just shocked, that's all!
Look!
Uh, great; what is it this time?
Weird.
I wonder what this steel barrel is doing here.
Uh. Yeah.
All right.
I vote you look inside.
Huh?
Are you scared?
Will you stop saying that?
I'll look.
It's not that big of a deal.
Ah!
That's what I was really worried about!
Takagi?
Where'd you run off to?
Quit messing with me.
Didn't she mention something about being spirited away?
But that couldn't...
Takagi!
Answer me!
What are you freaking out for?
It's just me.
Where'd you come from?
Hey.
You were looking for me just now, weren't you?
Huh? Yeah right.
Why would I do that?
So she lured me in here to jump-scare me a ton.
Whoa.
Look at that.
That's a big hole.
Why don't you take a peek inside it?
Like I'd fall for the same trick twice.
Don't make me laugh!
Oh no, I'm stuck!
My hand's stuck in the hole!
How do you like my acting?
I've been working on it.
I'm gonna freak you out so bad!
I don't know what, but it feels like
something's pulling me from the other side!
Help me...!
Nishikata.
Did I scare you?
No.
What is that?
I dunno, I found it on the ground.
Oh!
Glad your hand came loose.
Man.
I gotta find some way to get
her before we leave this tunnel!
As jumpy as usual.
Ahh...
Some fresh air!
This sucks.
I couldn't find anything to get her back with.
Must be another couple on a date in the spooky tunnel.
Don't bother them.
Let's go.
Okay.
She called it a "date."
She doesn't know what she's talking about.
Hmm?
What is it?
You're blushing again.
Did you have fun back there?
Because I did.
I guess.
Yeah, but...
It's almost noon, we should go back home soon.
Yeah, let's.
What way are you going?
You want to go back through there?
Yeah, why not?
Are you scared?
When am I ever?
I met my quota for the day.
Wait.
It's summer vacation.
Why do I still have just as many push-ups to do as normal?
"Summer Science Project"
Yes, the consommé flavor is quite good.
Don't lie.
Your eyes are watering.
No, they're not.
And I know it's better than your kelp flavor.
They both sound awful.
There are so many flavors to
choose from. Why would you pick those?
You wouldn't understand, miss watermelon.
Take risks while you're still young, right?
That's some philosophy to apply to popsicles.
Hey, did you two decide on
subjects for the science project?
Not yet.
Me neither.
You?
I'm still thinking, too.
Isn't there something easy I can do?
Like, finish-in-a-day easy?
Just do actual research.
Hmm...
A dog observation diary?
Ah! Awesome idea!
That sounds super easy!
And dogs basically behave the same way every day.
So I can just copy the entries and change the dates!
If you're gonna lie, write it by hand at least.
Besides, dogs barely do anything.
They wake up, bark for a walk, bark to
be fed, and sleep every chance they get.
Maybe they'll wake up and bark for attention,
but then they'll just bark for food again.
Why would anyone want to observe that?
You're such a stick in the mud, Yukari.
Well she is the class president.
It comes with the territory.
Right?
Shut up.
Anyway, have you two started to do your homework yet?
We've still got plenty of time.
Right?
Just so you know.
You're not copying mine.
Not even if I do your science project for you?
On a dog?
No, thank you.
You say this now, but you're gonna end
up sharing your answers with us anyway.
She wants the class to get good grades.
Right?
Maybe I should do an observation
diary on their procrastination habits.
"Water Tap"
So hot.
This is the worst day of vacation yet.
Are you kidding?
First, I overslept.
And then I had a flat tire.
But at least all this happened on a
day we're not practicing tandem riding.
Takagi said she was going on a family vacation.
When's she coming back from that?
I was gonna stay home for a few hours and
do chores, so I could have the afternoon free,
but of course I was sent on a shopping trip.
Truly this is the darkest of vacations.
That kinda sounded poetic, I should write it down.
That looks like...
Yeah, it's Takagi.
Huh.
I guess she's back.
I might as well use this opportunity to follow her.
Maybe I can find a weakness to exploit in the future.
Uh oh.
Did she see me there?
Maybe it was my imagination.
No, she did see me!
But I can see her hat sticking out around the corner.
You think you're gonna surprise me, don't you?
Not while I still may breathe!
I should write that down, too.
She... She got me!
Going somewhere?
Yeah.
Just grocery shopping.
Hey.
What a coincidence.
I am too.
We could take your bike, ride tandem?
Come on.
We agreed no doing that in the road.
When did she find out I was following her?
Fine.
Let's walk together, then.
Oh no! I gotcha!
Are you okay?
And the curse of today continues.
You're hurt.
Nah. It's nothing. I'll just let it be.
Don't do that.
You should wash it off.
How embarrassing.
Does your knee hurt that much?
No.
It's just that I was already having
a bad day, and now I got a cut, too.
I'm wallowing in how much this vacation sucks.
And it's not like I can write about
my misfortunes for my summer homework.
Here.
Huh?
But it'll stain.
Don't worry, just take it.
Uh.
Thank you.
That feels nice!
So you tried to catch me before, right?
Thanks for that.
You should come in.
The cold water's really nice.
Uh, No, I...
You know you want to.
Cooling you down?
Uh.
You know what?
I had a good day.
Because I got to see someone.
Huh?
Wh-Who do you mean?
You'll get your souvenir tomorrow.
Hey!
Stop that Takagi, the water's really cold!