RIHAN (VOICEOVER):
Seven-fold, eight-fold,
the Yamabuki rose blooms.
But not a single fruit it bears.
Such sadness.
[scream]
-Yuki Onna, what's wrong?
-Aotabo!
Kurotabo!
-What the hell's going on here?
-Huh?
-Wha--?
-I did it.
That went totally--
-Master!
-You're like the
Supreme Commander.
Your pranks go too far.
AOTABO AND KUROTABO: Master!
-Hey, is somebody going
to get me down or what?
NARRATOR: Rikuo Nura, age eight.
-That's very funny.
A yokai should never let
others get the drop on them.
-Hey, grandpa, does that
mean I can have the title?
I want to be Third Heir.
-Hm, wait a little longer.
-Longer?
-Maybe when you're a little
older and more like a yokai.
-Really?
I'll do my best.
I'll work hard so I can become
a great yokai leader like you.
NURARIHYON: Ha, ha, ha.
That's my boy.
-You know, I wonder if
yokai are that strong.
The ones at our house sure
don't look that way to me.
-What are you saying to me?
Don't you know about
my younger days?
-Tell me again, grandpa.
I love hearing about it.
-I had 100 yokai under me,
and did amazing things night
after night.
I was feared by
humans and revered
by yokai as the
Supreme Commander.
When people talk about the Lord
of the Night, they mean me.
-Awesome.
You're the coolest grandpa ever.
-All right then, Rikuo.
I'll show you some
more of my yokai magic.
-Mhm.
-Huh?
Weren't there customers here?
-Hm?
WAITER: Ah!
They punked us!
It's a dine and dash!
-This is a spell that
lets you eat for free.
-You're so cool, grandpa.
-Master.
-Master Rikuo.
ALL: Good morning to you, sir.
-Morning.
Out of the way, guys.
I'm going to be late.
[chatter]
I'll see you guys later.
ALL: Have a good day.
-Please be careful
out there, Master.
-I've got to hand it to him.
He really got us good yesterday.
-He's been going overboard with
the pranks the last few days.
KUBINASHI: That's a good thing.
-Huh?
-You should be happy to
see him so full of energy.
-Come on, don't act like
he didn't get you good too.
-Aotabo.
-Wah!
-Let's not talk about that, OK?
-Hey.
-Hold on.
-Hey, Kana.
-You're late, Rikuo.
The bus almost left without you.
-Sorry, it was the guys.
-The guys?
-That's right.
You ought to stop by and
visit one of these days, Kana.
You'd like everyone.
-I don't want to.
Your place kind of looks like a
haunted house from the outside.
To me
RIKUO: Really?
[starting gun]
TEACHER: 6.9 seconds.
-No way.
I lost again.
-We all lost to Nura.
You really have gotten
fast lately, Nura.
-I don't see any
difference between us.
It's not fair.
-Of course there's a difference.
My grandpa's the Supreme
Commander of the yokai.
ALL: The yokai?
-And so that's how the handsome
onmyoji swordsman defeated
the fearsome
child-devouring yokai.
And the shrine
built in his honor
is what's known today
as the Aratama Shrine.
The end.
CLASS: Oh.
-Hold on.
CLASS: Huh?
-Doesn't that story sound a
little bit strange to anyone?
[chatter]
-Huh?
What do you mean exactly?
-It's just-- it's just the yokai
should have been the good guys.
-Huh?
-What?
-What's that?
-Sure, they can kind of
be screw ups sometimes.
But Aotabo's strong,
and Yuki Onna's
a good cook even though
her food's always cold.
-What are you
talking about, Nura?
-He gets like this.
He'll say weird
things sometimes.
-So you're saying
there's something
wrong with Kiyotsugu's
report, is that it?
-Yeah, there is.
I know.
My grandpa's the Supreme
Commander of the yokai.
-Rikuo.
-Oh, then I guess that
means your grandpa has
to be Nurarihyon.
-Yeah, that's him all right.
You really know your stuff.
-Of course I know about him.
Nurarihyon's very well known.
He likes to go
into people's homes
and eat his fill
of all their food.
And then after he's
done that, he'll
go out of his way to purposely
make trouble for them.
He's the pettiest yokai ever.
-Gee, sounds pretty lame to me.
-Unbelievable.
-But don't worry, everyone.
Yokai are just fairy tales that
people made up a long time ago.
They don't really exist.
Hah.
NATSUMI: Yeah, that's true.
SAORI: It'd be scary if
they really did exist.
-Wait, hold on a minute.
You know, my house is full of--
-What's your problem, Nura?
Just let it go.
-There are no such
things as yokai.
-But I'm not lying.
-Moving on now.
Does anyone have any questions?
I'll be more than happy to
share all the little details
about my research.
-Hm?
What's wrong, Master.
You look like you're
feeling kind of down.
-Yeah, it's nothing.
-There's going to be a meeting
with all the clan leaders
today.
You should cheer up.
-Huh?
A meeting with the leaders?
-The Supreme Commander
wants you to join as well.
RIKUO (VOICEOVER): These are
all of the top yokai in the Nura
Clan.
They all look so strong.
They're so cool.
[clears throat]
-I've asked all the leaders to
come here today for one reason.
I've decided that
it's finally time
to name the clan's Third Heir.
[gasping]
It's been three years.
It's about time I did this.
I'd like to name the Third
Heir, in other words,
our next Supreme Commander.
-I think that's a good idea.
After all, you've been out of
retirement this entire time.
It's hard, isn't it?
-There isn't a
single yokai who can
compete against
Lord Gagoze's evil.
-Not to mention the fact
that the Gagoze group has
been responsible for all of
the missing children this year.
GAGOZE: Not at all.
I consider sending children
to the depths of hell my duty.
It's nothing special.
-What did you say just now?
Missing children?
You're saying you killed them?
-That's right.
And quite a few too.
-Evil's name is Lord Gagoze.
-He's such a paragon
of yokai virtue.
-That's nothing.
I started the fire
in Aratama Town.
-No way.
No way.
I don't believe it.
[clears throat]
-I see.
It sounds to me like you're
as active as ever, Gagoze.
-But grandpa--
-Yes.
You can leave everything to me.
-Even so, you're
not right for this.
-Huh?
-I was thinking
for our Third Heir,
that I'd name my
grandson Rikuo here.
-What's that?
-You're naming Master Rikuo?
-But he's still a child.
-He may have your
blood, but still--
GAGOZE (VOICEOVER): Is
he really choosing a brat
like that over me?
-What's the matter, Gagoze?
You don't look well.
-I'm just fine, I assure you.
-Hey, grandpa.
-Now what's wrong?
I thought you'd be happy.
You wanted this, didn't you?
-Huh?
-As my grandson,
you have the right.
In the end, you do take after
me, and everybody sitting here
knows it.
Come on, we're going
to put it to a vote.
Rikuo, I'm letting
you take over.
-No, grandpa.
-72 organizations
comprised of 10,000 yokai.
-I don't want--
-All of them will be under
your comman starting now.
-No!
[gasping]
I don't want this.
If I spend more time with
them, my friends at school
are going to hate me even more!
I never knew this 'til now.
I never knew how all the
yokai were such bad guys!
I'm not like you, grandpa!
I'm not like you at all!
-Huh?
What?
Wait, you Rikuo!
-Supreme Commander,
pardon my insolence,
but is Master Rikuo
really your grandson?
-Hm?
-I'm not only referring to his
appearance, but also the fact
that he seems to think
just like a human.
-It's quite a shame.
It seems the Young
Master would rather
be playing games like
other children his age.
[snickering]
KIYOTSUGU: What's
wrong, yokai boy?
Aren't you getting on?
-Don't give him any ideas.
If he gets on, we might
get attacked by yokai.
KIYOTSUGU: True enough.
[laughter]
-Jeez, what the heck are
you moping around for?
If you miss that bus, it'll be
30 minutes 'til the next one.
Just ignore them and get on.
-I'm fine.
And anyway, I don't
have the right
to ride the bus with them.
-Why not?
-Because I'm ashamed.
-Ashamed of what?
-I thought yokai were a lot
cooler than they really are.
But the truth is they're always
going around doing evil things.
They're nothing like
heroes, none of them.
And me, I've been trying
to be like my grandpa,
and he's the one who's
in charge of them all.
I'm so ashamed.
-I don't really get
it, but just become
someone you can be proud of.
-Huh?
-All you have to do is
become a good person.
One who can show them the way.
Isn't that right?
-A good person.
-Yep.
Let's go.
The bus is going to leave.
-That's OK.
I feel like walking home.
-You know, Rikuo, I
really don't think
you should say that your
grandpa's a yokai anymore.
-What?
That means you didn't
believe anything I said.
KANA: It scares me.
Yokai are ghosts, right?
-Scares you?
-I'd believe it if
you showed me some,
but I'd rather not
see any at all.
RIKUO (VOICEOVER): People really
do hate yokai, don't they?
That's it.
I'll never talk
about them again.
-Honestly, I came looking
for you out of concern
since you were late.
But to think you
intended to walk back.
You'll have to have
escorts from now on.
-Karasu Tengu, um, that is--
do you know whether I'm a human
or not?
-What?
I suppose so.
After all, both your mother
and grandmother are human.
-They are, aren't they?
-But at the same time,
a quarter of your blood
does come from the
Supreme Commander too.
-A-- a quarter of my blood?
-Oh look, the Master's back.
-Master, you're safe.
-What's the matter, everyone?
-The news.
Just look.
REPORTER (ON TV): We're
here live at the site
of a landslide that occurred
in the tunnel near Ukiyoe Town.
-What?
-Oh, Rikuo, you're home?
It's a lucky thing you
didn't take that bus.
-That bus they're
showing, is Kana on it?
-Hm?
-She needs help.
-Where are you going?
-The only place that matters.
I'm going out to save Kana.
Ao, Kuro, guys.
-Right.
-Just one minute.
I think not.
For you to leave and go
help humans is preposterous.
-What?
Why's that?
-Remember what our emblem is.
Our clan is about Fear.
We yokai are supposed to
inspire fear in humans.
Yet you wish to go help them?
It's absurd.
This is the home base
for this area's yokai.
We're the Nura Clan.
I won't allow the
Hundred Demons to be
commandeered on a human's whim.
-I think talking like that is
crossing the line a little,
don't you?
-You brute.
Do you have any idea who I am?
-Yeah, Lord Daruma,
our General Council.
-Aotabo.
-Hey, calm down.
-Aotabo, stop.
AOTABO: Shut up.
Didn't what he say
bother you too?
TSURARA: But Ao, if
you keep this up--
AOTABO: What?
What's going to happen?
TSURARA: Come on, Ao.
Would you calm down?
-How can I after that?
[arguing]
-Would you all stop it?
-Huh?
-I don't have time for this.
-Yes, sir.
-Master?
-I've never seen him like this.
What's going on?
-Listen, all of you.
-Master?
-Master's changing.
-I get it.
You're telling me that
being human is the problem.
But if I'm a yokai, you'll
follow me without question,
right?
If that's what you're
saying, then I'll
quit being human right now!
Something feels different.
My blood is boiling.
-That would be your yokai
blood, Master Rikuo.
-My yokai blood?
-Yes, your grandfather's.
A quarter of your blood comes
from the Supreme Commander.
It's not a lot,
but it means you've
got every right to
lead us, Master Rikuo.
-What are those guys?
-Could those things be yokai?
-That can't be.
Right, Kiyotsugu?
-Where is the Master?
-Well, he's undoubtedly
inside there somewhere.
In any case, we're going
to kill every living thing
down here, right
along with the Master.
[screaming]
-That's good, children.
Tremble with fear as we
devour your flesh, your skin,
your bones.
We'll feast upon it all and then
send you on your way to hell!
[screaming]
RIKUO: So killing kids
makes you a big shot?
-Who's there?
RIKUO: Gagoze, if
your whole plan
was to take over as the
Third Heir by killing me,
then I have to tell you--
you're one petty yokai.
-No, it can't be.
-Hmph.
-I don't believe it.
Kill him.
Kill the Master at once.
And kill those worthless
fools in the main family too.
Annihilate them all!
KUBINASHI: You won't
get a step closer.
It'll only get tighter.
-It'll take more than
that to bring down
Aotabo, the Strike Team leader.
-Let me remind you that you're
not the only Strike Team
leader here.
-I-- I don't believe it.
My clan is down.
My invincible army that's
killed countless others.
[screaming]
-Don't come any closer
or I'll kill them all.
If you want them alive, then--
[screaming]
-Master!
-Why?
Why a brat like you?
How am I not worthy?
In the entire clan,
I'm the most feared.
RIKUO: A yokai that
devours children--
that's scary all right.
However, I won't let a
yokai who takes pleasure
in killing the weak ever
become the Lord of the Night.
Not while I'm around.
I'll be the one who
will lead the clan.
And I will become
the Third Heir.
Anyone who tries to hurt humans
is going to answer to me.
-Master.
-All the world's
yokai will know this.
I'll become the
Lord of Pandemonium.
All yokai will fall
under my command,
in my Night Parade
of a Hundred Demons.
-Whoa, holy cow.
-So cool.
-Those were yokai.
They really do exist.
-I, Daruma, thought I knew this.
But have now realized what
a Lord of the Night is.
It is one who evokes
all, even among humans.
One who wears the
true mantle of Fear.
-Master!
Are you all right there, Master?
[scream] The Master's
turned back into a human.
NARRATOR: Four years later.
KARASU TENGU: All right.
Did all of you get one?
-Wow, all of them match?
AOTABO: I think this
is pretty awesome.
-They're getting
rather cocky out there,
the whole sorry lot of them.
Just because they performed
well against the Shikoku yokai.
-They needed something
to strengthen their bond
so they wouldn't get anxious.
It's been four years now
since he first awakened.
Even now, the Master
can only change
into a yokai for a short time.
-That's true.
A fool like that can't
possibly become the Third Heir.
-The most important thing for
a yokai is to gather Fear.
The Nura Clan's
influence is nothing
like it was long ago when
we were called the Night
Parade of a Hundred Demons.
However--
-OK, I got it, Kiyotsugu.
See you tomorrow.
A yokai on a samurai estate.
Sounds like it could
be interesting.
RIKUO (VOICEOVER): Yokai
will no longer run rampant,
not while I'm around to
keep an eye on things.
I will rebuild the Nura
Clan's Night Parade
of a Hundred Demons.
I'll see for myself
whether or not
this new yokai has what it
takes to join my Night Parade.
NARRATOR: The Young
Master of the Nura Clan
and candidate for the Third
Heir, Rikuo Nura, age 12.
[theme music]
-Yokai are absolute evil.
RIKUO (VOICEOVER): I will
be the Lord of Pandemonium.
KANA (VOICEOVER): Why do I see
his face when I look at Nura?
-He's a yokai.