>> THAT’S AS FAR AS YOU’LL GO!
WE’RE THE GUARDS OF
NIJO CASTLE’S EAST GATE!
GAITARO!
>> AND I’M GAIJIRO!
>> DID YOU GUYS THINK
THAT YOU COULD ACTUALLY
JUST STROLL ON IN?
>> YOU LOOKING TO DIE?
’CAUSE YOU’RE GONNA!
[ LAUGHS ]
>> THAT WAS EASY!
>> YOU RIPPED THROUGH HIM
LIKE HE WAS PAPER!
[ LAUGHS ]
>> OVER HERE!
>> WHAT THE HELL?
WHO ARE THEY SUPPOSED TO BE?
>> LISTEN UP, DEMONS
AND YOKAI OF KYOTO!
FOR THOSE OF YOU WHO DON’T KNOW,
THEY SAY THAT YOUR COMMANDER
AND OURS HAVE HAD A GRUDGE
THAT’S LASTED 400 YEARS.
SO I’VE COME HERE TO SETTLE ALL
OF OUR ISSUES ONCE AND FOR ALL.
AND I WON’T BE SHY ABOUT
SENDING WHOEVER’S IN THE WAY
ON A TRIP DOWN SANZU RIVER.
GET LOST UNLESS YOU WANT TO DIE!
>> HE’S SUCH A BAD ASS!
>> WHO TAUGHT YOU THAT WORD?
>> AND LOOK.
THEY GAVE US A HAORI.
ISN’T IT LOVELY?
>> FOCUS!
[ GRUNTING ]
>> THAT WAS CLOSE.
WELL DONE.
GRANDSON OF NURA, THERE’S A SPOT
CALLED NUEGAIKE POND NEARBY.
HAGOROMO-GITSUNEH
WILL GIVE BIRTH THERE.
>> NUEGAIKE?
>> I TRUST THAT YOU CAN FIND IT.
YOU ARE HIS GRANDSON, AFTER ALL.
>> RIGHT.
>> I DON’T THINK SO!
>> HE’S GOING TO USE
NENEKIRIMARU.
CAREFUL,
IT’S A HORIZONTAL STRIKE.
I SEE THEM.
EVERY SINGLE INTENTION.
IT’S ALL AS CLEAR AS DAY.
HE INTENDS TO CUT YOU DOWN
WITH A SINGLE STRIKE.
HE’LL BE SWIFT AS A GALE.
[ SHOUTS ]
>> COME AT ME ANY TIME!
>> I SEE IT.
I SEE IT ALL.
KYOKASUIGETSU!
THAT’S A PHANTASM.
HE’S SIMPLY USING FEAR
TO CREATE THE ILLUSION
HE’S THERE.
>> OH?
>> I SEE.
SLIP AROUND BACK AND
THEN STRIKE LIKE LIGHTNING.
OVER THERE!
>> DAMN IT ALL TO HELL!
[ GROWLING ]
>> I’M GONNA SWALLOW YOU WHOLE!
>> YOU BEAR A SLIGHT
RESEMBLANCE TO HER.
PRINCESS YO.
SHE WAS A LOVELY THING,
OF THAT THERE’S NO DOUBT.
THERE’S NO NEED FOR
THE PUZZLED LOOK.
SHE WAS YOUR GRANDMOTHER.
WE OFFERED MANY
BEAUTIFUL PRINCESSES
TO LADY HAGOROMO-GITSUNEH
AND NOW THE FRUITS
OF OUR EFFORTS ARE
AT LAST RIPE.
>> SO YOU’RE TELLING ME
THAT’S THE REASON
YOU KEPT KILLING
INNOCENT PEOPLE?
>> AND WHAT IF IT IS?
>> YOU GUYS DISGUST ME.
>> NURA!
>> YURA!
>> HUH?
>> WAIT.
I SENSE A VERY IMPULSIVE
WILL FROM HER.
SHE WILL SUMMON A HUMANOID
SHIKIGAMI WITHOUT A DOUBT.
DODGE IT.
>> BUKYOKU!
CUT THEM DOWN!
>> SO PREDICTABLE.
>> WHAT?
>> FOOLS LIKE YOU ARE
THE EASIEST TO DEAL WITH.
[ GRUNTS ]
>> YURA, DEAR!
>> OH?
I SEE, I SEE.
YOU’RE FURIOUS THAT ONE
AMONG US WAS ABLE TO KILL
YOUR GRANDFATHER.
WELL, AS AN OLD ONMYOJI,
HIS DEATH
WAS A MATTER OF COURSE.
YOU’RE THE PRODIGY?
YOU LOOK A LITTLE BONY,
BUT I BELIEVE I SHALL OFFER YOU
TO OUR LADY EVEN SO.
>> NOW STAY CALM, YURA.
HE WANTS YOU
TO LOSE YOUR COMPOSURE.
YURA, DEAR?
>> HUH?
>> I’VE HEARD ENOUGH!
I WON’T LET YOU GET AWAY
WITH SAYING THAT!
YOU GO TO HELL!
>> WHAT DO YOU INTEND TO DO?
HMM. CHARGE SHIKIGAMI.
OBLITERATE THEM BOTH.
NO SURVIVORS.
WHAT?
NO! THIS IS TOO MUCH!
THERE’S NOT ENOUGH TIME
TO READ HER MIND!
WHAT KIND OF MONSTER IS SHE?
>> YEAH, NO KIDDING.
YURA’S SOMETHING ELSE,
ALL RIGHT.
IF I’M NOT CAREFUL,
I’LL GET WIPED OUT, TOO.
>> WAIT! WE SURRENDER!
>> YOU SAID YOU COULD
READ MINDS, RIGHT?
THEN YOU SHOULD ALREADY
KNOW MY ANSWER.
[ SCREAMS ]
>> GOOD THINKING.
[ LAUGHTER ]
>> DOING THAT MADE
HIS MIND-READING USELESS.
>> HUH?
>> YOU’RE AN IMPRESSIVE DUO.
>> I SWEAR, WHAT
WORTHLESS AYAKASHI!
BUT AT LEAST THEY WERE ABLE
TO STALL THEM A LITTLE.
>> THEY’RE HERE,
BUT THEY WON’T INTERFERE,
NOT AFTER WE’VE COME THIS FAR.
THE TIME HAS COME TO FULFILL OUR
MASTER’S MILLENNIUM-LONG WISH.
>> MASTER RIKUO!
>> SO WE MEET AGAIN, BOY.
>> IT’S YOU, HUH?
KIDOMARU, RIGHT?
>> I COMMEND YOU ON
COMING THIS FAR.
HOWEVER, YOU WILL NOT
GO ANY FURTHER!
AFTER ALL, WHAT REASON
IS THERE TO OPPOSE
OUR LONGSTANDING WISH?
NONE IS EVIDENT TO ME
AND OUR DESIRE
HAS SPANNED A MILLENNIUM.
[ GROANING ]
>> AH!
>> MY LADY!
>> AT LONG LAST!
[ LAUGHS ]
THE MOMENT OF BIRTH
IS FINALLY AT HAND!
[ GRUNTS ]
>> MOTHER, MOTHER,
DELIVER ME
WITHOUT FAIL THIS TIME.
>> OH!
MY DARLING CHILD!
NOW I SHALL ONCE AGAIN BEAR YOU.
[ RUMBLING ]
[ SHRIEKS ]
>> WHAT’S GOING ON HERE?
>> IT BODES ILL.
COULD HER LABOR HAVE STARTED?
>> MOVE IT, MISTER.
>> NEVER!
OUR MASTER TOLD US
THAT COEXISTENCE BETWEEN MAN
AND AYAKASHI LIGHT AND DARKNESS
IS NOT THE IDEAL.
A WORLD ORDER WHERE
DARKNESS RULES OVER LIGHT IS.
>> DARKNESS OVER LIGHT.
>> I ASK AGAIN, FOR WHAT PURPOSE
DO YOU LEAD YOUR HUNDRED DEMONS?
WHAT CAUSE DO YOU UPHOLD?
AS A FELLOW AYAKASHI,
YOU SHOULD JOIN US
IN RESURRECTING NUE,
THE TRUE RULER OF DARKNESS.
THEN, AS A SERVANT OF
THE KYOTO YOKAI,
YOU COULD DEDICATE YOURSELF
FULLY TO THE CREATION
OF OUR IDEAL WORLD.
IF YOU REFUSE TO DO SO,
YOU’LL DIE RIGHT HERE.
>> I SEE.
DARKNESS RULING THE LIGHT.
SOUNDS LIKE AN INTERESTING IDEA,
TO TELL YOU THE TRUTH.
I’M A YOKAI, TOO.
IT MAKES SENSE.
>> MASTER RIKUO?
>> OH, THEN
WHY DON’T YOU FOLLOW US?
>> IT’S SIMPLE.
YOKAI ARE EVIL.
THAT MUCH IS TRUE.
WE COMMIT EVERY WRONG
AGAINST HUMANS
AND WE EXIST TO BE FEARED.
BUT WE’RE STILL DIFFERENT
FROM YOU GUYS.
>> WHAT’S THAT?
>> THE WAY YOU GUYS GO AROUND
KILLING INNOCENT PEOPLE,
ALL SO YOU CAN RULE OVER THEM,
THAT GOES AGAINST MY IDEALS.
THE LORD OF AYAKASHI SHOULD USE
HIS FEAR TO CAPTIVATE
ALL THOSE PEOPLE.
>> LONG AGO, SOMEONE COMPARED
THE DIFFERENCE BETWEEN KYOTO
AND EDO YOKAI TO FIRE.
THE YOKAI AND EDO
ARE LIKE FIREWORKS.
THEY USE THEIR FEAR
LIKE GUNPOWDER
TO BRIGHTEN THE SKIES
AND TO CAPTIVATE
THE PEOPLE THERE.
ON THE OTHER HAND, OUR FEAR
IS LIKE HELLFIRE
THAT BURNS IN THE DARK,
DESTROYING EVERYTHING
AND TERRIFYING HUMANS.
THE TWO ARE IRRECONCILABLE.
COME FORTH, RAJOMON GATE!
>> HUH?
>> WHAT?
WHAT THE HECK?
>> THE CASTLE DISAPPEARED!
>> WEIRD!
NOTHING’S HERE!
>> HEY, GUYS! LOOK!
>> HUH?
>> YOU STAND BEFORE OUR
FORMER HOME NOW, RAJOMON GATE.
AND I AS THE LEADER
OF THESE DEMONS
SHALL CONSIGN YOU TO OBLIVION
ON THIS VERY SPOT!
>> ALL RIGHT, THEN.
WHY DON’T WE PIT YOUR FEAR
AGAINST OURS AND SEE
WHICH SUITS KYOTO’S DARKNESS.
>> HERE THEY ALL COME!
>> COME ON, TSURARA!
>> HUH?
>> ARE YOU READY THIS TIME?
>> I AM!
OH!
>> I SEE.
SO YOU’VE MANAGED TO LEARN
YOUR FATHER’S TECHNIQUE,
HAVE YOU?
>> YOU KNEW HIM?
>> HOW COULD
I HAVE FORGOTTEN HIM?
OUR FEARS CLASHED MANY TIMES.
>> TSURARA, STAY BACK.
>> THAT TECHNIQUE
IT’S KNOWN AS EQUIP.
I SUPPOSE I CAN’T
TAKE YOU LIGHTLY.
I SHALL USE MY TRUE FEAR NOW.
IT’S OVER. DIE!
SLASH! THE PLUM TREE!
[ GASPS ]
>> THE BLADES OF MY PLUM TREE
ARE LIKE COUNTLESS BRANCHES
AND LEAVES.
YOU CANNOT POSSIBLY
DEFLECT THEM ALL!
>> KURO!
>> ARE YOU OKAY?
>> IT APPEARS THAT YOU’VE
LEARNED THE EQUIP TECHNIQUE,
MASTER RIKUO.
AND AT THE AGE OF 12, TOO.
YOUR PROGRESS AMAZES ME.
STILL, IT SEEMS
YOU’RE NOT USED TO IT YET.
ALLOW ME TO INSTRUCT YOU.
LET US SLAY THIS DEMON TOGETHER.
>> KURO.
>> EQUIP HAS A FEW VARIATIONS.
WHAT YOU JUST PERFORMED WITH
YUKI-ONNA WAS THE STRIKE METHOD.
WHILE POWERFUL,
IT LEAVES YOU OPEN.
IT’S SWIFT AND EFFECTIVE
AGAINST THOSE ATTACKING HEAD-ON.
THAT SAID, IT’S NOT SUITED
FOR CLOSE QUARTERS.
DANCE OF THE BLACK WEAPONS!
AND AGAINST ENEMIES LIKE THIS
ONE WHO USE RAPID ATTACKS,
IT’S USELESS!
>> KURATABO IS GOOD.
>> YOU’RE NURARIHYON’S GRANDSON.
OH, I WONDERED WHO IT COULD BE.
SO YOU’RE STILL ALIVE?
YOU’RE A HARD ONE TO KILL,
YOU MAGGOT!
>> KURO, TAKE CARE
OF MASTER RIKUO!
>> LISTEN CAREFULLY, MASTER.
THE OPTION TO TAILOR THE
TECHNIQUE TO SUIT YOUR OPPONENT
IS THE BEAUTY OF THE EQUIP.
I’LL EXPLAIN THE METHOD NOW,
SO USE IT TO EQUIP ME.
>> YOU DON’T SEEM TO BE
VERY FOCUSED ON THIS BATTLE.
>> MAINTAIN YOUR COMPOSURE.
DO EXACTLY AS I SAY, MASTER.
FIRST...
>> CHERRY BLOSSOMS!
>> WHAT?
HE’S CONSIDERABLY
FASTER THAN BEFORE!
[ SHOUTS ]
>> MY PLUM TREE IS LIKE
COUNTLESS LEAVES CLIMBING
TOWARD HEAVEN
AND MY CHERRY BLOSSOMS
ARE LIKE A VIOLENT STORM
OF FLOWERS BLOWING
THROUGH MT. YOSHINO.
THEY STRIKE 10 TIMES
FASTER THAN THE PLUM TREE.
>> 10 TIMES?
[ GRUNTING, COUGHING ]
>> THAT WAS CLOSE.
YOU OKAY, KURO?
>> I’M FINE.
I WAS JUST EXCITED
AT THE THOUGHT
OF BEING EQUIPPED BY
THAT LITTLE RASCAL I KNEW.
AND I SUPPOSE IT MADE ME
GET A LITTLE CARELESS THERE.
>> KURO.
>> NOW, YOUNG MASTER,
ONE MORE TIME.
>> RIGHT.
>> I’LL END THIS WITH
THE NEXT ATTACK AND
NOTHING WILL REMAIN AFTERWARDS,
NOTHING EXCEPT AN EMPTY VOID.
IT’S WITHOUT COMPARE.
THEREFORE, OBLIVION!
MY ATTACKS THIS TIME
WILL BE 10 TIMES FASTER
THAN CHERRY BLOSSOMS.
DIE!
>> LISTEN CAREFULLY.
WEAR MY FEAR AS YOU WOULD
A KIMONO AND JOIN YOUR MIND
WITH MINE IN THE MANNER
OF MEIKYOSHISUI.
>> WHAT?
HE BLOCKED MY SLASH ATTACK?
>> KURO, I’VE GOT
YOUR FEAR EQUIPPED,
THAT’S FOR SURE.
IT’S RAGING, TOO, AND TELLING ME
TO KILL THE DEMON HERE!
>> THERE’S TOO MANY OF THEM!
>> NICE!
IT’S LIKE A THOUSAND BLADES
OVERFLOWING ALL IN ONE SWING.
SO THIS IS THE SECOND METHOD
THAT MY OLD MAN USED.
>> IT’S NOT OVER.
NOT YET.
I WON’T ALLOW MYSELF
TO LOSE HERE!
[ GRUNTS ]
>> WHAT’S HE UP TO NOW?
>> BEHOLD MY SECRET
TECHNIQUE FOR MY MASTER!
FOR MY LORD SEIMEI’S
LONGSTANDING WISH!
>> A THOUSAND YEARS AGO
IN THE COURTYARD OF
ANCIENT KYOTO’S
IMPERIAL PALACE...
[ GASPING ]
>> WHAT IS ALL THIS, DOMAN?
>> YOU CLAIM SEIMEI BROUGHT
A CORPSE FROM THE GRAVEYARD,
BUT IT’S ALIVE!
>> EXPLAIN THIS!
DID YOU TAMPER WITH
THE SOUL REBIRTH JUTSU, SEIMEI?
>> I HAVEN’T A CLUE.
>> OUTRAGEOUS.
>> LOOK, KIDOMARU, DON’T YOU
FIND THIS CAPITAL BEAUTIFUL?
[ LAUGH ]
>> YOKAI FILL THE SKIES.
HUMANS LIVE IN HARMONY
WITH NATURE.
WHEN THEY SENSE
THE FADING LIGHT,
HUMANS GROW FEARFUL
OF THE DARKNESS.
I CREATED THIS BEAUTIFUL CAPITAL
WITH ITS PERFECT SYNERGY
BETWEEN YIN AND YANG.
I WANT THIS BALANCE
TO LAST FOREVER.
FOR THAT TO HAPPEN,
I MUST ATTAIN IMMORTALITY.
[ RAIN FALLING ]
>> THE SOUL REBIRTH JUTSU
HASN’T BEEN PERFECTED YET.
WHATEVER IS REVIVED
ENDS UP LIKE THIS.
HEAR ME, KIDOMARU.
I VOW TO RETURN TO THIS WORLD.
I WILL BE REBORN.
A PERFECTED SOUL REBIRTH JUTSU
WILL ENSURE THAT.
>> OH, WHAT A PLEASANT SURPRISE.
HAVE YOU COME TO VISIT ME?
MY BELOVED SEIMEI,
PLEASE COME CLOSER, SON.
>> OF COURSE.
AS YOU WISH.
>> IT WAS THEN THAT LORD SEIMEI
CAME TO A REALIZATION.
HE SAW THE KEY
TO THE SOUL REBIRTH JUTSU
AND HIS REVIVAL.
>> THAT’S THE ANSWER.
IF I’M TO RETURN, IT SHOULD BE
THROUGH YOU, HAGOROMO-GITSUNEH.
MOTHER, WILL YOU GIVE
BIRTH TO ME ONCE MORE?
>> WHEN HUMANS DIE, THEY ALWAYS
MOVE ON IN CYCLE OF REBIRTH
TO BE REBORN AS A PLANT
OR SOME OTHER LIVING CREATURE.
WHEN I AM TO PASS AWAY,
INSTEAD OF THAT CYCLE,
I’LL RETURN TO YOU,
YOU WHO LIVES FOR
MILLENNIA, AND FROM YOUR WOMB,
I SHALL BE REBORN.
THIS IS HOW MY TOTAL REVIVAL
SHALL BE ACHIEVED.
AND IT COMPLETES
THE SOUL REBIRTH JUTSU.
>> IT’S ALL CLEAR TO ME NOW,
MY BELOVED SEIMEI.
I SHALL GIVE BIRTH TO YOU ONCE
MORE AND OVER AND OVER AGAIN.
[ LAUGH ]
>> BEHOLD!
I WAS ABLE TO CAPTURE IT
AT LONG LAST!
THIS IS THE FOX THAT’S SAID
TO LIVE FOR THOUSANDS OF YEARS.
THEY SAY EATING ITS LIVER GRANTS
ETERNAL YOUTH AND LONGEVITY.
>> LORD SEIMEI!
>> WHAT ON EARTH ARE YOU DOING?
>> PLEASE FORGIVE ME, SEIMEI.
>> OH, MOTHER!
>> I CAN’T BEAR YOU NOW.
I LOVE YOU, MY SWEET SON.
>> YOU BASTARDS!
MY MOTHER WAS DEFENSELESS
AND YOU KILLED HER!
YOU’VE ALL BREATHED YOUR LAST!
IT’S CLEAR NOW THAT HUMANS
DON’T DESERVE TO RULE
OVER ANYTHING!
[ SCREAMING ]
>> HUMANS ARE FOOLS.
THEY DON’T KNOW THEIR PLACE
AND ENCROACH UPON THE DARKNESS
WITH LITTLE CARE.
IF LEFT ALONE, WHO KNOWS
HOW FAR THEY WOULD GO.
THIS BEAUTIFUL WORLD COULD
BE RUINED IN AN INSTANT.
FOR HUMANS AND AYAKASHI,
LIGHT AND DARK COEXISTENCE
ISN’T THE IDEAL.
THE DARKNESS MUST
RULE OVER LIGHT!
THAT’S THE WORLD’S TRUE ORDER!
>> OUR LONGSTANDING WISH!
[ CACKLING ]
>> IT’S ABOUT TO BE BORN!
>> I HAVE WAITED
A THOUSAND YEARS
FOR THIS POINT, THIS MOMENT!
>> WE FINALLY MEET,
HAGOROMO-GITSUNEH.