-I'm not your enemy, Jami.
Jami here was only
trying to protect you
from these bastards,
because you're
a direct descendant
of the master he
served when he was human.
-My my shikigami.
-Scum.
Impersonating a yokai.
What a joke.
[screaming]
Jami.
I could really use a
yokai like you around.
I will be the Lord
of Pandemonium.
I'm gathering my Night
Parade of a Hundred Demons.
-Lord of Pandemonium.
[theme music]
[sigh]
-We didn't get to
see a yokai again.
-Yokai or not, Shinako
still seemed grateful.
-And a lot more upbeat
than before too.
-She sure gave us a lot of
crabs to take back home.
-Shima, the legs are poking out.
-When the Kiyojuji
Paranormal Patrol shows up,
yokai know well
enough to steer clear.
-Steer clear, huh?
-All you did was
sleep in the hallway.
-Well, my eyes just
wouldn't stay open.
KANA (VOICEOVER): Kiyotsugu too?
I remember it got
cold last night
and then I just fell asleep.
Could that have been
the work of some yokai?
[giggle]
-Hold on.
What did you do to
them last night?
-You know, I've
been wondering why
Yura didn't tag along this time.
-Yeah, she is our lovely
neighborhood onmyoji.
-I wasn't able to get
in touch with her,
and she hasn't been
to school lately.
-Really?
I hadn't noticed.
-Jinchiki Synthesis!
-Hey, Kuro.
Let's hit one more bar.
-Sure, we can do one more.
-Just two for tonight?
-Yep.
-But I'll have to warn
you that all our girls are
too busy right now to
keep you two company.
-Huh?
Too busy?
-Yeah, we have some big shots
from the Nura Clan Strike Team
here today.
-Did you just say--
-The Nura Clan Strike Team?
-Yo, bring on the sake!
-Hey, hey.
I'm the famous Aotabo, and
I want to squeeze your jugs.
-No!
Well, OK.
-Kurotabo, at your service.
-You're cool, just like
all the rumors said.
Could you sign my chest?
-Be happy to.
[grumble]
-No way.
Are those two really--?
-Yep, it's Aotabo and Kurotabo.
GIRL 1: They say Aotabo is
the most powerful member
of the Nura Clan.
GIRL 2: I've heard Kurotabo's
one of the best-looking yokai
around, if not the best.
-I can't believe that
they're both here
and we get to entertain them.
-This is a once in
a lifetime chance.
-The power of the
Nura Clan's name--
-Is awesome.
BOTH: We're so lucky that
we look like those two guys.
AOTABO: Hey, Aotabo.
I've heard people
say that you've
slaughtered 1,000 yokai already.
-Huh?
-Why don't you show me
what you've got then?
Let's see how good you are.
-Ow, ow, what are you doing?
Stop it.
-How dare you deceive
people using my name, idiot?
-What?
It can't be.
The real ones?
-Huh?
You're fakes?
-Now that I see the real deal--
-They do look like knock-offs.
-We're sorry.
-I swear.
-Yeah.
Though I suppose it's
concrete evidence
that the Nura Clan's sphere
of influence has grown.
And it's all thanks
to Master Rikuo.
-Damn it all.
Things were going so good too.
-Who would've thought the
real ones would walk in.
-The yokai heroes of the Nura
Clan sure are something else.
-Clanless yokai
like us have to do
whatever we can just to get by.
It wouldn't hurt them to just
let us have a little more fun.
-Yep, totally with
you on that one.
-You aren't yokai by
any chance, are you?
-So that's the real Lord Aotabo
who's sitting in front of us.
-He's definitely big
and strong all right.
-I hope he doesn't
break anything.
-And Lord Kurotabo.
-He's so handsome in person.
-The local businesses
are all running again.
It's thanks to Master Rikuo
because he took Kyuso down.
-Hey, Aotabo.
What's your honest
opinion of Master Rikuo
and the future of the Nura Clan?
-Well, in the beginning,
I thought of him
as just the Supreme
Commander's cute grandson.
But then, he was
amazing that time.
I knew then that exchanging
Cups of Loyalty with him
wasn't a mistake.
Also he's still got room to
grow up and get stronger.
-But one flaw is that he can
only become a yokai at night.
And as a child, his
mind isn't that strong.
-Yeah, that's true.
That's exactly why we've got
to give him all of our support
so that he can become
a great leader.
-You're right.
Without a doubt.
-Yeah.
-Hey, is work all
you guys talk about?
-You're here now, so you
should be talking to us too.
-Butt out, ladies.
Go away.
-Lord Kurotabo, we'd like
to get to know you better.
-You're as manly
as the rumors say.
-Huh?
Hold on.
-Please don't interrupt.
This is very important for us.
-Do it later.
You're ours for
tonight, Lord Kuro.
-Or are you trying to say
that we're not important?
-I guess I really
don't have a choice.
-Why aren't any of the
ladies flocking to me?!
[screaming]
Die, Kurotabo!
KUROTABO: Hey, don't
destroy the place.
-Man, I'm pissed.
Why is he so popular
with the girls anyway?
I'm a Strike Team leader
too, just like him.
AOTABO IMPOSTER: Help me.
-You're that imposter.
-Please, help me.
-Well now, it's another one.
-Who are you?
What did you do?
-Destroy.
-What was that?
-Something exploded.
-Let's go.
We can't waste time here.
-What?
-Hey, who are you guys?
What the hell?
-Heh, you're a tough one.
Garo, devour.
-Hey, didn't you hear me?
I asked who the
hell are you guys?
Was that monster water?
-Mamiru, it looks
like lightning alone
isn't enough to finish this.
You're going to
need my water too.
Learn from your actual battles.
We are pros, yokai hunter pros.
-This is the Keikain Style.
Shikigami Fusion.
[screaming]
-What are you doing, Aotabo?
You let your guard down?
-My guard?
-I have no idea who
did this to you,
but you need to live up to your
name as a Strike Team leader.
-Humans.
-What?
Humans?
Funny.
Being drunk is no excuse.
-No, it wasn't the liquor.
Even sober, I still
would've lost.
They were so
powerful that I even
thought about taking
off my skull beads.
-I find that hard to believe.
If they had power equal
to that of a yokai,
they could only be--
-Onmyoji.
-Yura, are you here?
-Hey, Yura, where are you?
-Yoo hoo, Yura.
TSURARA (VOICEOVER):
Why do I have
to help look for
that onmyoji girl?
How did this happen?
[phone ring]
KIYOTSUGU (ON
PHONE): How goes it?
Any luck finding Yura?
-It's impossible to look
everywhere in town, you know.
KIYOTSUGU (ON
PHONE): No, it's not.
If you don't give up,
you're sure to find--
-He's being so unreasonable.
-It would be nice if we
could sense Yura's power
or something.
TSURARA (VOICEOVER): Oh please.
You guys are only human.
Huh?
Where's Master?
-Shoot, so close.
I still missed.
I'm worthless, worthless.
No, I shouldn't call
myself worthless.
I have faith.
I know I have the raw talent.
I've got-- oh.
No, what am I doing
thinking about him?
Focus, focus.
Yokai are enemies
I have to destroy.
-Miss Keikain?
So this is where you've been.
-Nura?
-I see now.
I thought you weren't
coming to school.
This is what you were doing.
It's summer break already.
-Are you alone?
-Huh?
-You're always with other
people, like Oikawa.
-Well, everyone's out
looking for you right now.
-Really?
-Yeah, they've all
been pretty worried
because they couldn't
get in touch with you.
-Worried?
I can't bear to face them.
I can't even protect
them from yokai.
I'm useless.
-That's why you're training?
I'm impressed, Miss Keikain.
-Huh?
-You know, most people wouldn't
have private training sessions
in secret like this.
That's a good quality to have.
It's appealing-- in
that I respect it.
-Nura.
YURA (VOICEOVER): Why do I see
his face when I look at Nura?
That's weird.
Is something wrong with me?
[stomach growling]
-Uh.
-That was not my
stomach, you got that?
-Here you go.
I had one left.
You like chocolate, right?
YURA (VOICEOVER):
What was I thinking?
There's no way Nura could ever
be connected to that yokai.
RYUJI: I finally
found you, Yura.
-What are you doing here?
-Who's he?
-My brother.
-What?
That's your brother?
-I followed the traces
of your shikigami.
I told you to keep in
touch with us, didn't I?
Oh, you're training.
Still, what are you
doing it here for?
-I-- I was--
-You could've just
walked on into town
and you would've run
into yokai everywhere.
So why train here?
-What brings you to
this town, big brother?
-Ryuji.
-There's only one
thing that brought us.
What onmyoji do-- destroy yokai.
-Look out!
Just what do you
think you're doing?
-Yura, who's this?
I asked you a question.
-Why does it matter?
He's just a classmate.
He's a friend.
-You aren't pulling
my leg, are you?
Don't tell me that
you haven't realized--
-No, don't say it.
-He's--
YURA: Stop.
RYUJI: A yokai.
You surprise me.
Every now and then,
little sister,
you can be really dense.
Come on, go.
What do we do to yokai?
Yokai are absolute evil.
So you know what
to do, don't you?
Garo, devour.
-Big brother.
-You should join in.
There's one thing I've
always taught you--
all yokai are evil.
You should destroy
them on sight.
RIKUO (VOICEOVER): He knows.
Now she does too.
It's all out.
-Still don't want to show
your true colors yet?
You're a yokai who took human
form to trick my sister.
It hurts me to do this when
you're still in human form.
But we must annihilate all evil.
-Hey, the sun's almost down.
-I think we'd better
head back now.
-Just a little longer?
TSURARA (VOICEOVER): Master.
Something's happened.
-Oikawa?
-Miss Keikain?
-What do you think
you're doing, Yura?
-Nura, you-- you
are a human, right?
-Miss Keikain.
I am.
I'm human.
-Right.
You heard him, big brother.
Nura isn't the enemy.
-Do you understand what
you just did, Yura?
Protecting a yokai is
against Keikain law.
You don't believe
your own brother?
-I believe Nura's
telling the truth.
We've only known each
other for a short time,
but he's my friend.
He's not an enemy.
I will not destroy him.
-Yura.
-If you hurt him, brother
or not, you'll face me.
-Face you?
Yura, take responsibility
for what you say.
Rentei!
Shikigami Convert.
Jinchiki Synthesis!
-Heh.
-Banish into the
Abyss, Yura Max!
-Yura, what's up with the
name of that technique?
Did you think of it yourself?
-Shut up.
It's my choice.
-Names are an important thing.
Garo, devour.
-Tanro!
RIKUO (VOICEOVER): The power
of the Keikain's is incredible.
-As always, your ability to
control multiple shikigami
at any given time is
an impressive thing.
You're right up
there with Mamiru
as far as your talent goes.
And that's a good thing for
you, for all Keikain's really.
However, even so,
you're too green.
YURA (VOICEOVER):
He released two?
-Those two are diversions?
-Huh?
-Can you see the real
one to your right?
[scream]
What's wrong, Yura?
There's another
one on your left.
YURA (VOICEOVER): There isn't.
It's to the right?
-It's too easy to mislead
you with a few lies.
-Miss Keikain!
Stop!
What are you doing?
You're her brother, aren't you?
-Quit acting so noble.
You're just a yokai.
YURA: Nura, I'm all right.
I won't lose to his shikigami.
And I won't lose to Garo.
What's going on here?
-Yura, you're letting words
influence you too much.
When my enemies
hear the name Garo,
they always expect an
aggressive shikigami.
But my shikigami's
real name is Gengen.
It's ultimate goal is to slip
inside my opponents' bodies.
Gengen, run.
[screaming]
There's more to the
onmyoji arts than just
using as many
shikigami as you can.
I hope you've learned that.
Manipulating your words
is also a good technique.
I can still forgive this.
If you want to live,
come back to us.
Bastard.
-I'm sorry, Miss Keikain.
I couldn't stand this.
-Is that you, Nura?
-I don't care if you're
an onmyoji or a Keikain.
I can't sit back and watch
someone harm my friend.
-So you've shown your
true colors, yokai.
It's over.
I'm the only one here who's
allowed to trick Yura.
[theme music]
RYUJI (VOICEOVER): Unnatural
beings, fade into darkness.
YURA (VOICEOVER): He
really is a yokai.
RIKUO (VOICEOVER):
Hagoromo Gitsune,
something about
this troubles me.
MAMIRU (VOICEOVER): Be
gone, into darkness.