[theme music]
-It's Gyuki.
-It's Mt. Nejireme's Gyuki.
-Who is your leader?
Because I, Gyuki,
will take him on.
-I always figured you
were the overeager type.
-Commander.
-The wolf.
I'd like a scarf.
-I'm honored I could help.
-Fall back!
Fall back!
-Get him.
-Take this.
-Show him not to mess
with the Nura Clan.
-Glorious.
-It is, Yuki Onna.
I mean, after all,
it is my clan.
-No.
I was referring to
you, Lord Nurarihyon,
my dear Supreme Commander.
-Now stop it.
Are you trying to kill me?
-Oh, one time isn't going
to be the end of the world.
Just one kiss.
-Another time.
It looks like things are over.
Excellent work, guys.
We beat them all.
-Yeah!
NARRATOR: During the Keicho
era, many ambitious yokai,
far and wide,
traveled to Kyoto--
which was known as a center
for yokai since ancient times--
to see who could reign supreme.
-That was a powerful group.
-So they're the Nura Clan.
-Yokai from all over Japan,
from the north to the south,
are gathering here.
We need to become stronger.
We need a greater power.
MAN: I beg you, Princess Yo.
Please save my son.
Princess Yo.
-It hurts.
It hurts.
-You'll be fine.
I promise.
The pain will fade soon.
-My goodness.
-Father.
-It's a miracle.
And all the doctors said
he wouldn't make it.
Princess, you are a
child of the gods.
Thank you so much.
Please accept this.
GUARD: Stop right there.
-Please, sir.
Please ask the Princess
to cure this child.
I beg you.
He'll die if she doesn't.
-No.
What point is there in
curing peasants like you?
-What point?
-Princess Yo, if
only she'd come.
-Her father will never agree
to help us, not without money.
-I have money for you.
-And who are you?
-If it's money you
want, I have some.
I'll happily give it to you in
exchange for something else.
-What is this?
-I want a liver.
[scream]
-Are you unhurt, my dear?
You're my treasure.
If you were to be
injured or die, I'd--
-I'm all right, father.
-I'm paying you a
fortune here so keep
those fiends out of the estate.
Is that clear, Lord Keikain?
-Perfectly clear.
I'll call my most skilled--
KOREMITSU (VOICEOVER): The
yokai glorifying human livers.
There are ancient tales in China
of yokai seeking Genjo Sanzo's
organs so they could
attain immortality.
Infants, priestesses,
princesses--
ayakashi believe that the
more precious the life,
the stronger it will
make their powers.
So that's what they pursue.
More ayakashi are looking
for human livers by the day.
I wonder if that
rumor is tied to it,
the one about the Lord of
Pandemonium nesting in Osaka.
PRINCESS YO: Poor thing.
FATHER: Increase the
number of patrols at once.
GUARD: Yes, my Lord.
-Princess Yo, the one
residing in that estate,
they say she has the power
to cure the incurable.
I hear that her beauty
is without equal.
And if you can manage to eat
a liver of a woman like that,
the power you'll gain
will be tremendous.
-Her liver.
Her liver.
-That human's liver will
help us conquer the world.
-Princess Yo, huh?
PRINCESS YO: Exorcist Blade?
-The sword imbued
with onmyoji power.
Every time the sword cuts
a yokai, it grows stronger.
The number of those
that desire your power
grows daily, Princess.
Please, carry this just in case.
-Very well.
-If you'll excuse me.
-How did it all come to this?
Father has changed as well.
All because of my power.
-So beautiful.
Who would've thought that
a mournful look could
be so attractive
in the moonlight.
-A thief?
How did--
-It was true.
Like they said, a
drop-dead beauty.
-What?
-I want you, Princess Yo.
PRINCESS YO: No, let me go.
What-- what are you doing?
-Karasu Tengu was right.
You're a gorgeous woman.
PRINCESS YO (VOICEOVER):
An ayakashi?
Is he after my liver?
This can't be.
-No!
-I thought that
you were fragile,
but you're pretty--
Hold
on, that's a Spirit Blade?
-Good.
It stopped.
-Just what are you?
KOREMITSU (VOICEOVER):
Yokai aura.
It can't be.
KOREMITSU: Princess,
are you all right?
-Nurarihyon.
-What?
-That's what everybody calls me.
Princess, you're not boring.
I'll be back.
KOREMITSU: Did something happen?
Princess.
-N--nothing at
all, Lord Keikain.
I'm fine.
Thank you though.
KOREMITSU (VOICEOVER):
Did I imagine it?
But still--
-Princess Yo.
-So that's the situation.
The streets are teeming
with lawless ronin gangs.
There are muggers
and kidnappers.
And on top of that,
it's said that they
have been eviscerating
infants as well.
HAGOROMO: There's no need
to report such details.
-Of course.
-We, the Toyotomi family, are
facing grave circumstances
at this time.
Our plan to fight the
Tokugawa-- it's ready, yes?
-Lady Yodo, Osaka Castle is
rumored to-- [clears throat]
There are reports of
yokai coming and going.
-What?
-This may have an impact
on our family's reputation.
-Don't tell me you actually
believe in such nonsense.
-No.
I'm certain that it is
merely wild speculation.
-It must be.
To think, with
Hideyoshi dead now,
the Toyotomi already find
themselves on the road to ruin.
His successor
Hideyori is so inept,
we've no hope of
ruling this country.
As it stands now,
our plain will fail.
We need more power.
If the Tokugawa rules Japan,
then yokai will suffer.
That much is certain.
-Lady Yodo.
-Yes, that's the answer.
For the sake of this unborn
child, I need a greater power.
Search for it, and
bring it here-- a liver
from a nobler human.
One worthy for me,
Hagoromo Gitsune.
KOREMITSU: Princess, is
everything all right?
PRINCESS YO: Yes, it is.
I am fine.
-If anything happens,
please summon me at once.
-I will.
Thank you.
KOREMITSU (VOICEOVER):
It's a minuscule amount,
but I sense some yokai
aura around the Princess.
No.
There exists no
yokai who can break
though our reinforced barrier.
Unless it's--
-Every day is stifling.
-The onmyoji are working
hard, just like last night.
-How is it you're getting in?
Where did you get my
father's pipe from?
-It's nice.
And I assume it
cost a lot of money
too, which his caged
bird earned him, right?
-Don't talk like that.
It can't be helped.
It is my destiny after all.
-Hey, you want to go out?
-Huh?
-You do.
You're suffocating here, right?
-I can't.
It would trouble others.
I couldn't possibly
go outside the estate.
I must stay here, for
the sake of my family,
as well as for my father.
Besides, there are
guards outside.
-Ow, the arm that
you cut is acting up.
-What?
-It looks like I've got you.
-You tricked me, you ayakashi.
-Hey, calm down.
I'm just going to borrow
you for one night.
Be back by morning.
-But--
-Don't struggle, Princess.
If anything, you're
going to enjoy this.
-Father?
My father and all the
guards, they don't notice us.
-That's because they're
dealing with Nurarihyon.
-Even in the street.
-Yeah, no one's
going to notice us.
Don't worry, you can just relax.
Trust Nurarihyon.
-Nurarihyon?
-Yes.
It's a free yokai's name.
Why don't you live
the way you want?
YOKAI: Whoa.
-So that's her.
-The one the Supreme Commander
went to try and seduce?
-The number one beauty in Kyoto.
-Well, what do you think?
-I'm at a loss.
She's even more
beautiful than they say.
-Are you jealous, Yuki Onna?
-Jealous?
Don't be ridiculous.
-Uh, they're ayakashi,
isn't that so?
-Don't worry about them.
They all work for me.
-Hey, you.
I hear you're a
real sheltered girl.
-I'll show you a
good time, Princess.
-Hold on, Lord Ayakashi, wait.
Don't go.
Whoa, nice one.
Is this your first time?
-50 points.
You're winning this game.
-You're amazing, Princess.
-Oh, no.
It was purely by luck.
-OK, I'm up next.
-Hey, it's my turn next.
-My money's on Princess Yo.
-Heave ho.
Heave ho.
-I swear, just what is the
Supreme Commander thinking?
-Bringing a human woman
to a yokai gathering.
It's unheard of.
-Does he plan to eat her liver?
-Who knows?
It's anyone's guess.
-That's funn.y
-Oh, come on, Lord Nurarihyon.
Why don't you and I have a drink
over there, just the two of us?
Huh?
Wait, hold on.
-Having a good time?
-Oh, I guess.
It's nice being out like this.
-Princess Yo.
-Yes?
-Let's become man and wife.
-Hold it right there for just
one minute, Supreme Commander.
What did you just say?
This woman is a human.
Do you mean to tell us that
you intend to marry a human?
-Nurarihyon.
Just what do you
see in this woman?
-That isn't the issue
at hand, you know?
-Setsura.
[gasp]
-Princess Yo is actually
a much better person
than you think she is.
-Don't-- don't use my given name
like we're all intimate now.
You're a pervert.
-Yuki Onna, you can't go
around saying that-- ah!
-I'm going to kill you!
[screaming]
You dummy!
You can just die!
NURARIHYON: Princess.
-What?
Yes?
-You've got a special
place in my heart.
I've watched you
for a long time now,
and my feelings have
only become stronger.
-But I--
-To put it bluntly, I've
fallen hard for you.
Princess Yo, become my woman.
-Wha-- what?
What was that?
I thank you for tonight.
-Hm.
-I thought you might
not bring me back here.
-Well, I keep my promises.
I'm not one of those
yokai who lies.
-I guess not.
If anything, you're
actually brutally honest.
-Come on.
Be with me.
I'm going to rule the world
one day, and to do it,
I need you there.
-Lord Ayakashi.
-How about it, Princess Yo?
-I'm sorry.
I'm not the person
that you think I am.
I have never helped
anybody unconditionally.
I ask you, if you want my
power, then please just go now.
-It's not your
power that I want.
I'm saying that I
want you near me.
I'll be back tomorrow.
-No, don't bother.
[coughing]
-So how are you doing now?
-Damn her.
Even my lungs are frozen.
I just can't believe the
Supreme Commander either.
Wanting to marry a human.
It's unheard of.
-It's exactly for that reason
that we all follow him.
KARASU TENGU: True,
he's unconventional.
He could become the
Lord of Pandemonium.
GYUKI: That's the
Nura Clan all right.
We've grown large enough to be
the Night Parade of a Hundred
Demons.
-But even so, I
didn't think we would
get to Kyoto this quickly.
GYUKI: If she felt like it,
she could easily come this way.
-Yes, Hagoromo Gitsune,
the great yokai
among yokai in Osaka Castle.
I hope the Nura Clan hasn't
reached its pinnacle too soon.
-So at this time, we would
like Princess Yo as a concubine
to Lord Hideyori Toyotomi.
FATHER: What a
large sum of money.
The Toyotomi family- it's
beyond what I'd hoped.
Well done, daughter.
-Your thoughts, sir?
FATHER: Wait, I spent so
much time raising her,
and she possesses
supernatural powers.
I'll hold out for more money.
-This is quite an honor.
It's just that being a mere
concubine would be such a pity.
SATORI: Oni
Hitokuchi, he intends
to milk us for everything.
-I see.
It isn't good to be
too greedy, you know?
Fine then.
Just take it.
There's your precious money.
-If you weren't so greedy,
you would still be alive.
-Sir.
-What?
Yokai?
-How?
You broke our barrier?
-What's that?
Are you talking about this rope?
-Please forgive us for failing.
We just couldn't hold on.
-No, even if I
wasn't here myself,
the main family's
onmyoji should have--
NURARIHYON: What's all this?
-You're Nurarihyon.
So the slight yokai aura
I was sensing was yours.
-Never mind that now.
Where's the princess?
-If they weren't acting
under your orders,
then it was other ayakashi.
-And they were
after Princess Yo.
Some human liver worshipers?
Where the hell did they go?
-They're at Osaka Castle.
-If she's there, then--
-Hagoromo Gitsune.
[theme music]
NURARIHYON (VOICEOVER:
I'm coming, Princess Yo.
KOREMITSU (VOICEOVER):
Hagoromo Gitsune
is no ordinary ayakashi.
HAGOROMO (VOICEOVER): A yakuza?
PRINCESS YO (VOICEOVER):
Lord Ayakashi!
NURARIHYON (VOICEOVER: I'll
cut down anything in my way.