>> HUH?
>> ITAKU?
WHAT TOOK YOU GUYS SO LONG?
I WAS STARTING TO WORRY
THAT YOU HAD RUN BACK TO TONO.
>> DON’T BE SUCH A MORON, RIKUO!
YOU OUGHT TO BE STRAIGHTFORWARD
IN TIMES LIKE THESE
JUST LIKE YOU WERE IN TONO!
JUST SAY YOU WANT OUR HELP!
>> RIGHT.
I’M COUNTING ON YOU GUYS.
>> SIX, HUH?
ARE YOU GUYS DONE TALKING NOW?
WE’RE TRYING TO FIGHT HERE!
>> STAND BACK, YOU GUYS!
NUMA-KAPPA NINJA ART,
SLUDGE HELL!
[ LAUGHS ]
IT’LL BE HARD TO FREE YOUR ARM
NOW THAT IT’S CAUGHT IN THERE.
I WONDER IF IT’S
STICKIER THAN YOUR WEBS.
[ GRUNTS ]
[ LAUGHS ]
>> I FELT THAT ONE.
GUESS I’D BETTER ADD YOU
TO MY TOP 10 LIST OF
HEAVYWEIGHT YOKAI.
IT’S GONNA TAKE SOME TIME
TO BEAT YOU.
>> LET’S DO THIS!
>> RIGHT!
>> RIKUO.
WE HAVE A SCORE
TO SETTLE WITH TSUCHI-GUMO TOO.
SO IF YOU DON’T FEEL LIKE
FIGHTING HIM, THEN WE TONO
WILL TAKE HIM DOWN INSTEAD.
>> YOU CAN’T BEAT TSUCHI-GUMO
WITH A FEW SCATTERED ATTACKS.
>> WHAT?
>> MASTER RIKUO, I STILL
REMEMBER THE FEELING
OF THAT TECHNIQUE.
RELEASING EVERY OUNCE OF
MY FEAR WAS EXHAUSTING,
BUT EVEN SO, AS A PART
OF HIS NIGHT PARADE OF
A HUNDRED DEMONS,
IT’S MY DUTY TO SERVE HIM!
MASTER RIKUO, LET’S DO
THAT THING AGAIN!
>> HUH?
>> THAT, UM...
>> LISTEN TO HER!
NO MATTER HOW STRONG
THE TONO ARE--
[ GASPS ]
>> YEAH!
>> WHEW!
>> THIS IS RIDICULOUS!
HOW STRONG IS THIS GUY?
>> LET’S DO IT, MASTER RIKUO!
WE HAVE TO USE EQUIP AGAIN!
>> WHAT? EQUIP?
WHAT THE HECK’S THAT?
>> THE TECHNIQUE THAT
DESTROYED TSUCHI-GUMO’S ARM.
>> ARE YOU SERIOUS?
RIKUO DID THAT?
[ SHOUTS ]
>> YEAH, BRING IT ON!
TO TELL YOU THE TRUTH, I WANT
TO SEE YOU TRY THAT AGAIN!
>> HEY, IF YOU HAVE A TECHNIQUE
LIKE THAT, THEN JUST USE IT!
WHAT’S IT LIKE?
>> YOU HAVE TO RELEASE
YOUR OWN FEAR AND
ENTRUST IT TO RIKUO.
IT ISN’T POSSIBLE
WITHOUT MUTUAL TRUST,
BUT IT MAGNIFIES
THE POWER SEVERAL TIMES OVER.
>> SO MY FAITH IN
MASTER RIKUO BECOMES HIS POWER.
>> GOT IT!
THEN I’LL DO IT WITH YOU!
>> HUH?
>> LOOK, I LIKE YOU, RIKUO,
SO THAT’S GOOD ENOUGH, RIGHT?
>> HUH? WHAT?
>> PLUS, I WANT TO KNOW WHAT
KIND OF TECHNIQUE THIS IS.
SO COME ON, SHOW IT TO US.
>> HEY, ARE YOU SERIOUS?
>> YOU’RE DAMNED RIGHT, I AM!
LET’S DO THIS. EQUIP ME.
>> OKAY, THAT DOES IT!
THERE’S NO WAY HE CAN!
I’M THE ONLY ONE...
>> HOLD ON, RIKUO.
CAN YOU HANDLE DOING IT TWICE?
I SURE COULDN’T.
>> YOU’RE JUST A BIT SHORT
IN THE STAMINA DEPARTMENT.
I’LL BE FINE.
>> HE PERFORMED EQUIP
WITH LORD ZEN, TOO?
BUT, MASTER, I THOUGHT I WAS
THE ONLY ONE YOU COULD PERFORM
THE TECHNIQUE WITH!
>> LISTEN, I’VE NEVER
SEEN YOUR FEAR BEFORE.
I DON’T KNOW WHAT’S COMING,
SO WE CAN’T DO IT.
>> I SEE.
>> TSURARA, LET’S GO.
RELEASE ALL OF YOUR FEAR FOR ME.
>> I’LL HAVE TO DECLINE.
>> HUH?
HEY, TSURARA?
>> I’M SORRY, MASTER!
I JUST CAN’T RIGHT NOW!
>> IT’S THAT EXHAUSTING?
>> WATCH OUT!
THE WIND KNIFE!
>> AH!
>> WELL, WHAT’S THE PLAN?
>> YOU REALLY ARE
SOMETHING ELSE.
IT’S YOU I WANT.
>> HUH?
>> LEND ME YOUR POWER.
LET ME EQUIP YOUR FEAR.
>> RIKUO, DO I HAVE
TO REMIND YOU?
I DON’T TAKE ORDERS
FROM ANYONE, EVEN YOU.
BESIDES, I CAN’T ENTRUST
MY FEAR TO YOU.
THAT SOUNDS TOO DAMNED RISKY!
WHAT ARE YOU DOING?
>> I’VE GOTTEN A LOT BETTER,
HAVEN’T I?
SO BECOME MY BLADE, ITAKU.
[ SIGHS ]
>> THAT’S WHAT I WANT.
>> IF YOU MESS UP,
I’LL KILL YOU.
RIKUO, YOU IDIOT!
YOUR BACK’S WIDE OPEN NOW
AND I TOLD YOU
NEVER TO UNDO YOUR FEAR.
WAIT A MINUTE!
THAT’S NOT IT!
HE’S CARRYING MY FEAR!
>> YOU READY?
LET’S GO!
>> RIKUO IS--
>> HE’S CARRYING ITAKU’S FEAR!
>> SO THAT’S
THE EQUIP TECHNIQUE?
>> HEH.
YEAH.
>> LET’S END THIS!
>> AND SEE WHICH OF US
IS STRONGER!
YEAH!
>> I TOLD YOU TO
MAINTAIN YOUR FEAR!
>> YOU’RE ALL INCREDIBLY STRONG.
IT’D BE PERFECT
IF YOU GUYS JOINED ME.
>> THE TONO ARE MERCENARIES.
A LOT OF US HAVE SIDED
WITH WEAK COMMANDERS BEFORE
AND LIVED TO REGRET IT.
WE ONLY ACCEPT THE STRONG.
>> ITAKU, BECOME MY BLADE.
EQUIP.
INDIGO ASTER SCYTHE!
[ GRUNTS ]
>> ITAKU!
>> SO DID WE GET HIM?
[ GROANS ]
>> HE’S STILL STANDING?
>> YEAH!
THAT’S IT!
DODGING THAT ATTACK WOULD
HAVE BEEN SUCH A WASTE!
IT’S NOT EVERY DAY
I GET TO ENJOY THIS.
IT WAS A TASTE WORTH SAVORING.
YEAH!
>> NO WAY!
>> TSUCHI-GUMO GOT SPLIT
RIGHT IN HALF!
>> WE WON?
>> IT’S TERRIBLY NOISY OUTSIDE.
>> WHAT?
I DON’T HEAR A THING.
I UNDERSTAND, MY LADY!
I’LL GO CHECK.
>> THAT WON’T BE NECESSARY.
>> HUH?
WHO’S THERE?
SHOW YOURSELF!
>> IT’S BEEN A LONG TIME,
HAGOROMO-GITSUNEH.
>> IT’S YOU!
>> YES.
IT’S THE ONE WHO KILLED YOU
THOSE 400 LONG YEARS AGO.
>> THE YAKUZA...NURARIHYON.
>> IT LOOKS LIKE YOU’VE CHOSEN
A YOUNGER BODY THIS TIME.
VERY NICE.
IT LOOKS SEXIER THAN THE ONE
YOU WERE IN BEFORE.
IS THIS WHERE YOU’LL GIVE BIRTH?
>> WHAT’S THIS?
TIME HAS CERTAINLY
NOT BEEN KIND TO YOU.
>> MY LADY!
>> WAS IT YOU?
WERE YOU THE AYAKASHI
WHO KILLED OUR SECOND HEIR?
[ PANTING ]
>> MASTER!
>> OH, IT’S YOU GUYS.
YOU’RE LATE.
[ GASPING ]
>> MASTER RIKUO,
YOU’VE DEFEATED HIM?
PLEASE FORGIVE ME!
I WASN’T HERE FOR YOU.
I’M ASHAMED TO FACE...
>> I KNOW THAT I’VE MADE THINGS
HARD FOR EVERYONE
AND ALL BECAUSE
I WASN’T STRONG ENOUGH.
KUBINASHI, KAPPA, KEJORO,
KURATABO, AOTABO,
NEXT TIME WE’LL ALL FIGHT.
>> MASTER RIKUO.
>> TSURARA?
SAME GOES FOR YOU.
>> RIGHT!
[ GIGGLES ]
UH, I DON’T REALLY CARE.
>> MAN, RIKUO.
>> YOU SURE ARE A PLAYER.
>> THAT WAS SOME FIGHT.
>> HUH?
>> DARKNESS SHALL ONCE AGAIN
REIGN OVER THIS WORLD.
MY LONGSTANDING WISH
IS ABOUT TO BE FULFILLED.
COMPARED TO THAT,
WHO I’VE KILLED HOLDS
LITTLE IMPORTANCE,
NEXT TO NOTHING.
>> YOU HAVEN’T CHANGED
A SINGLE BIT, HAVE YOU?
I CAME ALL THE WAY HERE
TO CHECK THINGS OUT
FOR MYSELF, BUT IT’S CLEAR NOW.
THERE’S NO WAY FOR YOUR KIND
AND MINE TO GET ALONG.
>> WHAT’S WRONG?
NOT FIGHTING?
>> SORRY, BUT I’M TOO OLD
FOR THAT NOW.
AND TAKING YOU ON WOULD BE
A BIT OF A STRETCH FOR ME.
YOU’LL PAY FOR
THE SECOND HEIR’S DEATH, THOUGH.
MY GRANDSON WILL SEE TO THAT
AND HE’LL STOP YOUR PLANS TOO.
DON’T SAY I DIDN’T WARN YOU.
[ LAUGHS ]
>> DID YOU REALLY THINK YOU
WOULD LEAVE ALIVE, NURARIHYON?
>> ACTUALLY, I DID,
HAGOROMO-GITSUNEH.
[ LAUGHS ]
>> OH!
>> MY LADY!
>> MOTHER.
>> HUH?
>> HURRY, HURRY.
MORE, I WANT MORE.
[ GROANS ]
>> HURRY, HURRY.
>> THIS IS BAD, VERY.
>> MASTER RIKUO!
HE’S STILL--
[ CRASHING ]
[ SHOUTING ]
>> IT’S BEEN A THOUSAND YEARS.
NOBODY’S BROUGHT ME DOWN
TO MY KNEES SINCE NUE.
>> NO WAY!
>> HE ISN’T DEAD YET?
>> NUE?
IS THAT THE ONE?
THE KYOTO YOKAI’S
LONGSTANDING WISH?
>> THAT’S RIGHT.
I’VE BEEN ITCHING TO GO HEAD
TO HEAD WITH NUE AGAIN
FOR A LONG WHILE.
>> OH, THERE, THERE.
BE PATIENT, MY BELOVED CHILD.
THIS OLD MAN’S DEATH MUST COME
FIRST AND, AFTER THAT,
YOU SHALL HAVE YOUR MEAL.
>> WHAT IS THIS STRANGE
AND EVIL FEAR I FEEL?
ONE THING’S FOR SURE.
WE HAVE TO STOP
THIS BIRTH SOMEHOW.
[ GROANS ]
>> WHO EXACTLY
IS THIS NUE ANYWAY?
>> IT’S ANOTHER NAME
FOR A MYSTERIOUS CREATURE
WHO’S KIND OF HARD
TO DESCRIBE.
>> MYSTERIOUS?
>> THAT’S RIGHT.
HE’S BEEN BOTH AN AYAKASHI
AND A HUMAN BEFORE.
HE RULED KYOTO’S DARKNESS
A THOUSAND YEARS AGO
AND THAT MAN WAS AN ONMYOJI.
>> WHAT DID YOU JUST SAY?
>> YURA?
>> HE WAS HUMAN AND ONMYOJI?
JUST WHAT DO YOU MEAN BY THAT?
TELL US THE WHOLE STORY!
HOW CAN NUE BE AN ONMYOJI?
ONMYOJI ARE ON
THE SIDE OF HUMANS!
>> THE HUMANS’ SIDE?
>> YOU’VE GOT TO BE KIDDING ME.
MORE DAMN BUGS HANGING AROUND.
>> I WAS DISTRACTED
BY THAT FEAR, SO I DIDN’T
NOTICE HIM THERE.
[ GRUNTS ]
>> YOU CAN’T RUN.
>> WHY IS THAT YOU
ALWAYS SHOW UP?
>> AS IF A GUY LIKE HIM
WOULD BE ON ANYBODY’S SIDE.
HE JUST USES PEOPLE!
>> USES THEM?
HOW?
>> IT CAN’T BE.
>> ANYWAY, I’M GOING
TO SLEEP UNTIL NUE’S BORN.
OH, AND RIKUO, I HAD FUN TODAY.
SEE YOU.
LET’S DO THIS AGAIN.
[ SCREAMING ]
>> FIGHTING ISN’T ABOUT
WHO WINS OR WHO LOSES.
CRUSHING ONE ANOTHER,
THAT’S WHAT’S FUN!
[ LAUGHS ]
[ COUGHING]
>> WE WON, BUT HE SURE
DOESN’T MAKE IT FEEL THAT WAY.
>> HIDEMOTO!
>> YES.
WE ARE MOST ASSUREDLY
RUNNING OUT OF TIME.
>> WHY ARE YOU CONSTANTLY
GETTING IN OUR WAY, NURARIHYON?
>> I’M COMING, MY LADY!
>> HUH?
>> LADY HAGOROMO-GITSUNEH,
WHERE DID THAT INTRUDER GO?
HUH?
I’M GOING TO EAT YOU!
[ LAUGHING ]
>> MOVE ASIDE!
>> YOU’RE IN THE WAY,
GASHADOKURO!
>> RIGHT IN THE NICK OF TIME.
>> I TOLD YOU BEFORE
NOT TO BE SO RECKLESS,
SUPREME COMMANDER!
JUST BECAUSE OTHERS CAN’T EASILY
ENTER THIS CASTLE DOESN’T MEAN
THAT YOU SHOULD!
>> FORGIVE AN OLD MAN.
I MEANT TO LEAVE RIGHT AWAY,
BUT I GUESS WHEN
IT COMES TO MY ONLY GRANDSON,
I’M A LITTLE OVERPROTECTIVE.
>> A LITTLE?
>> BUT HER NEW HOST...
>> SIR?
>> WE MUST ASSEMBLE
THE CLAN LEADERS IMMEDIATELY.
QUIT SCATTERING ALL THOSE
FEATHERS!
>> IT WASN’T ME.
SOMETHING’S WRONG WITH MY EYES!
[ GROANING ]
>> KARASU-TENGU!
[ SHOUTS ]
>> SUPREME COMMANDER!
[ LAUGHS ]
>> THIS BLADE’S TASTED
ALL THREE NURA HEIRS.
OUR MASTER’S TIME IS
JUST AROUND THE CORNER.
[ GROANS ]
[ LAUGHS ]
>> WHAT A PITIFUL END FOR
THE MAN ONCE KNOWN
AS THE LORD OF PANDEMONIUM.
HIS AGE IS FRIGHTENING.
[ LAUGHS ]
>> SUPREME COMMANDER!
>> IT’S THE DEVIL’S BLADE.
WHAT’S THIS BLASTED SWORD DOING
IN YOUR HANDS, YOU BASTARD?
>> HE DISAPPEARED!
>> AND JUST WHO THE HELL
ARE YOU EXACTLY?
>> YOSUZUMI!
>> GOOD.
MY SIGHT IS STARTING
TO COME BACK.
I’LL BE SURE
TO REMEMBER THAT EYE.
>> ARE YOU ALL RIGHT?
>> TASTED ALL THREE NURA HEIRS.
WAS RIHAN KILLED BY THAT BLADE?
AND THAT EYE...COULD IT BE?
>> MINAGOROSHI-JIZO?
>> HUH?
IT SEEMS HE GOT AWAY.
>> DID HE?
HE CAN’T GO FAR WITH THAT WOUND.
HAVE THE MOAT SURROUNDED.
>> RIGHT.
>> MINAGOROSHI-JIZO,
LADY HAGOROMO-GITSUNEH HAS
JUST ENTERED LABOR.
THE BIRTH SHOULD BE
TAKING PLACE AT ANY MOMENT NOW.
[ LAUGHS ]
>> AT LAST!
>> LORD KIDOMARU!
THERE’S A NIGHT PARADE COMING
DOWN HORIKAWA RIVER STREET!
>> WHAT’S GOING ON HERE?
>> YOU STAY RIGHT HERE, RIKUO.
ALL RIGHT, GUYS, LET’S GO.
IT’S WAR.
>> DAD...
>> YOU GO TO HELL!
>> YOUNG MASTER,
JOIN YOUR MIND WITH MINE.
>> SURRENDER TO US, KYOTO YOKAI,
OR PAY THE CONSEQUENCES!
>> GET LOST UNLESS
YOU WANT TO DIE!