RIKUO (VOICEOVER): Hagoromo
Gitsune has Princess Yo.
-Nurarihyon.
RIKUO (VOICEOVER): Her sword.
-I'm coming, Princess Yo.
[theme music]
-Supreme Commander,
where are you going?
-Gyuki.
-Supreme Commander, if you
go running off like that,
you'll draw attention.
This isn't like you.
Where do you intend
to fight tonight?
-At Osaka Castle.
You don't have to come.
-Osaka Castle?
You're joking.
I'm sure you know who
waits there, don't you?
Hagoromo Gitsune
is no mere Yokai.
-I've heard.
-She's the great
Yokai who's lived
in the capital
since ancient times,
so powerful she can
even rule over humans.
Stop this.
It's not the time yet.
You must gather strength as
the next Lord of Pandemonium.
-Enough, Gyuki.
If you're trying to say Hagoromo
Gitsune's the current one,
then all I have to
do is surpass her.
[screaming]
[gulping]
-It is different from
an average liver.
The baby's pleased too!
[chuckling]
-She-- she killed
Princess Miyako!
-So we are going to
be eaten after all.
The future I foresaw
is coming true.
Let me out!
I beg you!
[growling]
-Ayakashi.
I see my future.
These ayakashi
are going to-- No!
-Princess Sada.
[gulping]
-Tears made out of pearls?
I knew it.
Every one of the
princesses brought here
possesses some kind of power.
They want her livers.
-There's no need to be
afraid, Princess Yo.
Your flesh and
blood will live on
as part of the foundation of
our millennial Yokai capital.
Resign yourself,
my lovely princess.
-Lord Ayakashi...
You're here.
-What's this?
An intruder?
-Who might you be?
-A yakuza?
-I'm nurarihyon, the Supreme
Commander of the Nura Clan.
Sorry, but that's my woman.
I'm taking her back.
HAGUROMO GITSUNE:
What's all this?
A Yokai rescuing a human?
What an odd thing to do.
Are you a deranged
lone rat of some sort?
-Hey, guys.
So you decided to join.
-We are your Night Parade.
-Wherever you go,
we shall follow.
-You're a bunch of fools.
-We seem to have many
odd guests, insects
who don't know their place.
Who among us shall
make this show
an entertaining one for me?
-Allow me that honor.
I am [? gairota ?]
from Rashomon.
Remember this name as I send
you to the depths of hell!
Lightning Club Hurricane!
They've all blow
away without a trace.
-That was rather brief.
-Gairota!
-Move it.
I'll cut down
anything in my way.
-Follow the Supreme Commander!
-It's a free for all!
[chuckling]
-It's fun babysitting
the Supreme Commander.
If we live through this, let's
have another drink or two.
-Don't falter, just
focus on the present,
and you'll have nothing to fear.
-Don't worry about us, Gyuki.
We're all originally
born from the darkness.
None of us fears death.
We'll either lead our commander
to victory or die trying.
-Very well said, Hitotsume.
-What are you all doing?
Show them what a superior
class of ayakashi is like.
-Kill those who defy
our dark mother.
-I don't think so.
-Such child's play!
-You're Gyuki from Mt.
Nejireme.
-Mt.
Kurama's Great Tengu?
-Ah.
You look well, but the
child prodigy, Ume Wakamaru,
has grown up a fool,
if he's opposing us.
I suppose it can't be helped
under a reckless leader who
doesn't know his limits.
-That's true.
Our commander does march
to a different drum.
However--
-Hm?
-That's what makes him fun.
-Get behind me, and stay
out of sight, princess.
-Hey!
Calm down.
Easy.
-Princess Yo, Princess Yo!
She's in trouble.
-Lord Ayakashi.
-What an amusing show.
Having such fine
actors is a rare thing.
It's been a hundred years
since a Yokai opposed me.
-Get your hands off my woman.
Now!
-Oh.
Have you fallen
in love with her?
This play has some
rather unexpected twists.
Does this princess have the
power to enchant an ayakashi?
If so, it makes me want to
taste her liver even more.
-Princess Yo!
-Hidemoto, Hidemoto,
are you there?
-What's the rush, Koremitsu?
-We've lost many
from the main family.
-Even from here I can tell
what's going on in Kyoto.
Those barriers of yours could
never stop a powerful ayakashi.
-They were no good at all.
-And after 28 years of training.
-Get rid of them now, Hidemoto!
-Ayakashi do live
for hundreds of years.
You shouldn't
worry about losing.
You two, return.
-The ayakashi that
you were interested in
has headed to Osaka Castle.
-Him, huh?
He's the only Yokai
who would ever
come eat at an onmyoji's home.
He's a funny one.
But he can't kill
Hagoromo Gitsune.
What's he up to?
-Wait.
Where are you going?
-Osaka Castle, to observe him.
-Wha?
-Want to come too?
-Look at Osaka Castle.
The Night Parade of a
Hundred Demons is there.
-So it's true.
The Yokai had access to it.
-It's the end.
-The Toyotomi and Yokai?
I must tell Master Tenkai.
-What?
Is that it?
It seems you're just a weak
ayakashi like all the others.
This is a side show.
Entertain me.
Can you see how
many tails I have?
That's how many times
I've been reincarnated.
Now they react to any hot-headed
ayakashi who comes after me.
What's wrong?
Don't you want to save her?
Dance.
I shall enjoy watching you
dance to your last breath,
young ayakashi.
-Lord Ayakashi!
-Hagoromo Gitsune is
no ordinary ayakashi.
In turbulent times, she
emerges and possesses children.
She waits until the
moment their nature
becomes darkest, and takes
them over, aging them.
She absorbs all their malice,
and becomes more powerful.
Her life lasts as long
as humans' though.
So when her host's
life comes to an end,
she goes into hiding until
another suitable host appears.
-A rebirth Yokai.
You can't defeat her unless
you seal her real body.
She'll just return
across the eras.
-Wearing people
like Hagoromo robes,
always seeking to
disrupt the capital.
And that's where
she gets her name.
What worries me is
that she's collecting
all those human livers.
She's clearly planning
something, something very big.
-Can that ayakashi you're
interested in defeat
somebody like her?
-I don't think he stands a
chance, even one in a million.
-So then--
-However, he has one thing.
And that's room for growth.
He did gather that Night
Parade of a Hundred Demons
in only a century.
-Lord Ayakashi!
-I think not.
I'm aware of your powers, and
that just wouldn't be fun.
-Stop it.
Why are you doing this?
It's senseless.
I don't understand you at all.
Going this far, is this the
way that all men behave?
-Oh, you say such
adorable things.
Listen.
In this world, there are many
intelligent men, both ayakashi
and human.
You chose poorly.
It's unfortunate that your
first should be stupid.
Especially since he
is your last as well.
-Princess, how do I seem
to your eyes right now?
Do I look as stupid
as she just said?
When I think about you, princess,
my heart fills with joy.
-What?
-You're like a
cherry blossom to me,
so beautiful and so
delicate, yet so innocent.
You give peace to
all those around you.
And just having you by my
side will make everything else
seem brighter.
I see it now, that future.
-The future?
You mean you and me?
RIKUO: You seemed so
miserable when we met.
I'll make you happy.
How about it?
Standing before
you now, do I look
like a man who could
make you happy?
I doubt I do.
I have to show you
how great I am,
if I want you to fall for me.
I almost forgot myself,
trying to impress you so much.
It's time that you gave
her back, Hagoromo Gitsune.
HAGOROMO GITSUNE
(VOICEOVER): What's this?
He changed suddenly.
-Lord Ayakashi.
-Let's go.
The darkness starts know.
The real battle of Ayakashi.
HAGOROMO GITSUNE:
My tails aren't
reacting even though
he's right there.
I can't see him.
-My spirit blade?
-That won't work.
What-- What kind
of a sword is that?
It's fading away?
My Yokai energy, it's fading!
Wait.
Don't go!
The power I collected
for my unborn child,
for my precious baby!
Come back here!
How long do you think it
took to gather all this!
-Lady Yodo!
-What in hell did
that bastard do?
-Princess Yo!
-Commander!
We'll all take care
of everything here.
You go after her, and make
sure you finish her off!
-Gyuki, keep her safe.
-Don't let 'em escape, men!
-You're gonna have
to face us first.
-Yes.
That's right.
Keep going.
Go, and become the
Lord of Pandemonium.
Race to the top, Commander!
-You swine.
Do you have even the slightest
inkling of what you've done?
It took years to
gather that much power.
And it's gone now,
thanks to you.
I don't expect this to
restore my lost strength,
not with just your liver.
Even your entire
life won't be enough.
This side show is over now.
-Hidemoto.
-Shikigami Hagun,
Twelve Ancestral gods,
defeat the demons
and cleanse the evil.
God of the Eastern Sea,
Ame; of the Western Sea,
Shukura; of the
Southern Sea, Kyojo;
of the Northern Sea, Gukyo;
gods of the Four Seas.
Hagoromo Gitsune's powers
are fading quickly.
To think he weakened
her this much.
-Mind your own business, please.
Who do you think made
that sword you're using?
It cuts well, right?
Only Yokai though.
She's all yours, Nura.
-So is this gonna mean
that I owe you one now?
-Stop!
What are you doing?
Who do you think it is
you're dealing with?
Damn you!
You'll pay for this.
I swear that you'll pay!
A curse on you, a
curse, nurarihyon!
For the crime of
destroying my dream,
I will make certain you suffer.
I curse your bloodline
for all eternity,
for generations to come!
Your children,
your grandchildren,
they'll all be bound
by this fox's curse!
-He actually defeated her.
Guess this makes you the
new Lord of Pandemonium.
-Lady Yodo!
[sobbing]
-Without their leader, those
ayakashi will probably scatter.
And if I act now, I might
be able to defeat you too.
What now?
What does the Lord of
Pandemonium intend?
The Tokugawa's world is bright,
and darkness will definitely
fade.
It'll be a hard place
for Yokai to exist.
-You don't have to tell me that.
I know what's gonna be like.
And that's why I'm gonna be
the master of all those Yokai
who might fade Away
-To protect ayakashi, huh?
You'll accept humans, and
protect ayakashi world?
Coexistence?
That'll be hard.
-I don't think so.
I'll just have to
become invincible.
-You're unbelievable, you know?
-Lord Ayakashi!
-Princess Yo, what
are you doing there?
-Lord Ayakashi, your wounds.
-Hey!
-Are you all right?
-I was worried, Lord Ayakashi.
Please rest.
I'll stay here, and
heal your wounds.
These and any future ones.
-Coexistence, it could
happen with this ayakashi.
[laughter]
-It was a complete victory.
-The Nura Clan's invincible!
-Invincible!
-No holds barred
tonight, right, Gyuki?
-Even if it takes generations
to do, I'll get his kiss.
-This princess seems
to fancy me now.
-You're a suave one, Hitotsume.
-What-- what is all this?
-Thanks for hosting!
-Hey, get over here!
-Let's make some room
for the loser brother.
-This is the Keikain
Clan's main estate!
Why are Yokai here?!
-You won't be popular
if you're grumpy.
-Yeah.
-Hidemoto!
-I see.
So you're going back.
-Unlike that female fox, I'm
not interested in this land.
I've got the title I wanted
now, so I'm going back to Edo.
-I'm thinking of
trying something.
If it succeeds, it'll
be a strong barrier.
Even Hagoromo
Gitsune wouldn't be
able to a thing for 400 years.
Still, I'll be dead
and gone in 50 years,
so that isn't really my concern.
-50 years, huh?
A humans life isn't that long.
This could be the
last time we meet.
-Who knows?
I may become a Hagun,
and see you someday.
I wonder how powerful
he'll become.
Shame I won't be
around to see it.
-All right.
-Supreme Commander!
-What took you so long?
-Help me, Lord Ayakashi.
-All right, guys.
We're all done with Kyoto.
So gather around behind me.
We're going home.
[cheering]
[theme music]
-Without power, you're
stuck here until you die.
-I need to know.
Hagoromo Gitsune's
in Kyoto, isn't she?