[theme music]
-Hey, quit dragging
your feet there, Rikuo.
-Hey, could you guys
slow down a little?
-In your dreams.
You know what?
You're really useless when
you turn into a human.
-I'm doing My best.
Maybe we should have just
taken the train back.
AWASHIMA: You moron.
Like yokai could ride the train.
Just pick up the pace.
-Awashima, wait.
Huh?
Whoa.
-It's faster this way.
RIKUO: Hey, wait.
Quit it, Itaku.
This is embarrassing.
-Hey, are we getting attacked?
-Huh?
-So this is the Nura
Clan's base, huh?
-It's a lot bigger
than I pictured.
-We finally made it.
-Good All this sweat's
melting me way.
-It's Master Rikuo.
-You're right.
It is master.
-He's back home!
-Anyway, we're in
the right place.
-It was a long trip.
-Is there a swamp here?
-Hey, Rikuo.
It's nighttime
now, thanks to you.
-He couldn't help that.
He's human during
the day after all.
-Even so--
-And you turn into a weasel.
-They were really cute together.
-Who the hell are they?
-They're awfully casual there.
-Welcome home, Master Rikuo.
-Who might you be?
Only members of
the Nura Clan are
permitted into the main house.
-Wow.
They actually call him master.
-They really spoil him here.
You got a problem, monk?
We're not looking for a sermon.
-How dare you mock the Nura
Clan strike team leader.
-Hey.
I don't care who you are.
But don't treat me
like some woman!
You got that?
-Woman?
Sorry I-- I didn't
realize you were a lady.
-For now.
-Huh?
-Hands off, perv!
-What was that for?
-Ha.
You oversee the Kanto
region from here?
So where do you guys
usually go to train?
-Hey!
Off the cherry blossom tree,
-You know, you smell bad.
-You don't sugarcoat
things, do you?
I'm gonna give you a
little taste of hell!
-You stink!
-Aw, hey.
This isn't a swamp.
Who are you?
I'm a numakappa.
Name's Amezo.
-Huh?
Me?
I'm a kappa too.
My name's uh-- I've
never thought about it.
-You know, this rock is
pretty good for training.
-Wha?
Who in the world are they?
-And what do they
think they're doing?
-Master Rikuo?
-What's the meaning of all this?
-They're my friends.
I'm gonna go tell Gramps
that I'm back now.
Look after them for me.
-Are they yokai from Tono?
-Master, you're going to Kyoto?
-Of course.
Those who've swore their
loyalty should get ready to go.
-Rikuo, so you're back now.
-Yeah.
-Did you learn anything?
-Hard to say.
Well I get what a
Nurarihyon is now.
That's something.
-I see.
So--
-Let's right.
I'm leaving for Kyoto.
-Hm?
-Not bad at all, Rikuo.
I guess you can do
what you want then,
just bring back some
yatsuhashi treats.
-So you're not
against it anymore?
-Go, and cut out
threads of fate.
When you get back,
you'll be the Third Heir.
Oh, right.
When you get there, you
should see Hidemoto.
-Hidemoto?
And who's that, Gramps?
-You should ask
that onmyoji girl.
-Plan a victory banquet.
I'll be back.
What's all this?
Looks like you guys
are getting along now.
-He's back.
-That was fast.
-Should we get going now?
-Of course.
We're hitting the road.
-Hold on.
-Really?
What is it?
We're trying to leave here.
-I want to show you
something special first.
It won't take long.
They came the minute
I called them.
-What?
What is that?!
-Allow me to present
our strategic yokai
airbase, the Treasure Ship,
and our [inaudible] house boats
too.
For centuries
they've been pretty
handy to have on long journeys.
Rikuo, Kyoto really is
something else, especially when
you have a chance to see
it from up in the skies.
-Wow.
-Man, I'm impressed.
They sure don't look weak to me.
-Hey, Gramps.
I never knew about this.
-We're here!
Look, Shima.
The signs white,
not the usual red!
And Nowson's is black on white!
That's Kyoto for you.
They've got an eye for style!
We're finally in
the old capital!
Everyone, welcome to Kyoto!
-Someone's peppy.
-I wanna be a Mito girl.
-We made it.
-We're short a few,
but isn't it exciting?
I can't wait to get started.
-You mean Rikuo?
Forget him.
KIYOTSUGU: DOn't you worry.
I'm sure Nura will
catch up later.
-You think so?
By the way, why are we starting
off this trip at night?
-It's a yokai tour, Ienaga.
-A yokai tour?
KIYOTSUGU: There's no point
in investigating temples
and shrines when it's crowded.
IENAGA: I shouldn't have come.
-It's creepy wherever you look.
Can't you just feel
all the yokai aura?
-I think so.
It's so cool here.
-I've done a lot of
research about Kyoto.
Records show that 234 people
jumped off [inaudible] Temple!
And 85% of them survived.
-Wow.
KIYOTSUGU: 85%, Shima.
SHIMA: That's amazing.
-Hold on.
Where did Tori and Maki go?
They're not here.
-Huh?
The restroom maybe?
[chuckling]
-We're in the luck, brother.
-Fresh, human livers
on the menu again.
New Kyoto's a fun place.
[laughter]
-Huh?
-What?
-Hey.
That lantern there,
it's still lit.
-What was that?
Ienaga, that's a--
a Tadamori Lanter.
-Tadamori Lantern?
What's that?
-Well it's a legend
here at Kusaka Shrine.
Tadamori saw a lantern, and went
to dispatch the yokai holding
it, but it was
really a watchman.
-Oh.
-Doesn't that sound like
a suspicious lantern?
Let's go check it out.
-Hold on there.
It's the opposite of that.
-Huh?
-He's just jumped
to conclusions.
There's actually no yokai
in the legend, is there?
-You're absolutely right!
What a huge mistake.
There's no reason for
us to be here then!
-Kiyotsugu.
-Dummy.
-Shima, call her.
-Huh?
-Call Yura, and ask her to
come pick us up right away.
-Are you saying that you
didn't book any rooms for us?
KIYOTSUGU: Of course not.
He family's here.
-Hey, we're done here, right?
Let's--
It's glowing.
I'm scared. It's like I'm
going to be swallowed up
by the darkness.
-There's another one around,
just like our brother said.
-Yeah.
It's been a good night for
us, one feast after another.
-Yokai!
-Not so fast.
You're the main entree.
-You should be honored.
[chuckling]
-Get down!
-Ayakashi infesting
Kyoto, sink into darkness!
Explode!
[screaming]
-Run for it!
What were you doing?
We sent out a warning to
not walk around at night!
-Wait.
I know that voice.
Yura?
-You're so slow.
Ow.
I oughtta leave you behind.
-I'm coming.
Don't get so worked up.
The map said Kusaka
Shrine, right?
-Worked up?
If something happens
to them, we won't
be able to face Master Rikuo.
-I guess it does feel kind
of dangerous around here.
-The ayakashi invasion of
Kyoto is getting so bad
that it's beyond the
onmyoji's control.
I should have stopped them,
or gone along with them.
-Is that Yuki Onna?
-Look.
It's the onmyoji girl.
She's all yours!
-What's going on here?
-Kurata?
-Why'd you come, yokai?
-We had to, for Master Rikuo.
-How could you onmyoji
let Kyoto get this bad?
-You're one to talk.
Go ask your own kind, yokai.
-Tori, Maki!
-Gather all around
and freeze, my minons.
A cold greeting for our guests.
-Shikigami Rentei,
become my strength,
and vanquish the
darkness before me!
[chuckling]
-We'll devour you all!
-We're Kyoto yokai!
-Whoa.
That was close.
What's going on here?
Why are they attacking
humans out in the open?
I heard the rumors about
Kyoto, onmyoji girl.
Have things really
gotten this out of hand?
-Yura?
Is that Oikawa with you?
-Maybe.
-You OK?
-Yura?
What perfect timing.
We were just about to head
on over to your place.
-Hey, where's the restroom?
-Why are you all here?
This isn't a good
time to be in Kyoto.
-Huh?
What do you mean?
-Kyoto is about to the
overrun by ayakashi.
-Is that true?
Your brothers, Keikain Clan's
top three onmyoji are all dead?
-I don't know.
It all happened
inside a barrier.
But we can't find them, and
the Third Seal's broken.
ayakashi are now able to
enter the city as they please.
It's not safe.
-What exactly does
this all mean?
-Right now, the ayakashi
are only active at night,
so the Keikain Clan has issued
a general warning to stay away
from shrines and
temples after dark.
-And we headed
straight for one too.
-But it the two remaining
seals really do get broken,
and they enter into
new Nijo Castle,
then that's the
point of no return.
That's just what I predict.
The entire city will be
swallowed by darkness.
If that happens, ayakashi could
run rampant through Kyoto, no.
Through all of Japan!
-I-- I didn't know
how bad it was.
I should cancel the yokai tour.
YURA: It's a good thing I was
training in Madoyama park.
-Training?
-Mhm.
Although I can't say I've
completely mastered it.
But this isn't the time
for second thoughts.
In any case, you
should be safe here.
-Hey, where are you going?
-Don't tell me.
-To Sokokuji Temple.
They'll be there tonight.
-You don't have to go.
-I'm with her.
You're still just a kid, Yura.
-Some of us haven't fought.
Some chose to save
their own lives.
Still, we are onmyoji
of the Keikain Clan.
We face our enemies,
and we don't run away.
-But Yura--
-Oh no.
You know, now that
I think about it,
we're stuck here
in onmyoji central.
-Oh shit.
You're right.
-I mean--
-Don't mind us.
We're just-- Master Rikuo,
please come quickly.
-Amazing.
-Yura, we have a duty
to protect Kyoto.
Do you understand, Yura?
It is the duty of those
who possess the gift.
YURA (VOICEOVER):
Akifusa, He taught me
what it means to be an onmyoji.
He's the most gifted of us all.
I still can't believe
he was defeated.
I hope he's alive somewhere.
-It's them!
They're here!
A barrier has them.
-All right.
Stay focused.
-Damn this thing.
I can't get through.
What's going on!?
-This is a Fukuju Style
Barrier created by 30 men.
it won't break so easily,
unless my weapon is what's used.
-Stand strong!
Remember what
happened to Masatsugu!
MAN: They broke
through the barrier!
-But that's impossible.
-Well, well.
it's Yura.
-Masatsugu, my son
is still alive.
-Masatsugu!
Pato!
Are those-- you're kidding me!
-Hey, look.
The onmyoji are scared
out of their minds.
-Let's just get on with this.
I can't wait!
-We're gonna skewer every
single one of you onmyoji.
-Their barrier is gone.
Go.
Kill them all.
-Akifusa?
-Why is he helping
out the ayakashi?
-Our joint barrier
has collapsed!
-Switch to individual ones!
-There's no time!
-How did you?
-It went right through.
Look at that.
This is awesome.
Their Kekkai Barrier
is like paper.
This is gonna be so easy.
YURA: Shikigami Tanro,
Shikigami Rokuson, Bukyoku.
Stay back!
-No way.
She summoned all those
Shikigami on her own?
-Are you serious?
-That's amazing.
-They're coming!
-What is that?!
-An elephant?
-An elephant Shikigami?
YURA: Hyoman, keep going!
-Impressive as always.
You're able to summon so
many at one given time.
You're indeed a prodigy.
-Akifusa, tell me.
What happened?
It's crazy.
We have to stop them.
They're yokai, right?
Fukuku Style's about defense.
They're helpless
without their barriers.
-The yokai received
weapons that grow in power
the more they use them, from me.
-How could an onmyoji like
you lend his power to yokai?
Snap out of it, Akifusa!
-Yokai are darkness,
and we are light, Yura.
-You're the one who
taught me that one truth!
-You're wide open.
-He got me.
I'm finished.
-Gengen.
You overdid it.
You don't stand a
chance against him
if you divide your strength.
-Big brother.
-He's the worst one who
could have turned against us.
We can't hold out until
sunrise 27th Heir.
How long can you
maintain those Shikigami?
-If it's just three or
so, until morning time.
-Your willpower's
ridiculous, as always.
In any case, protect our allies.
RYUJI (VOICEOVER): I'm
probably a better choice
for this fight anyway.
-Big brother?
-Yura, Mamiru's
at the rear gate,
but he should be here soon.
Tell him this--
find the mastermind.
He must be watching
from the darkness.
He's the one who
corrupted Akifusa.
YURA: I knew it.
So that means one
of the ayakashi
is controlling Akifusa.
-Not quite.
It's thanks to the Yaso Style.
Its nature was like
that from the start.
It's a gray one.
-A gray one?
-He's coming.
Go, Yura.
-Ryuji.
I never thought that
you'd protect Yura.
-Well the thing is,
it's about talent.
You're really good,
but she's better.
-Ryuji, you've always
disapproved of me, of the way
I do things, of my
passion as an onmyoji!
And you know, I've always
longed to stand face
to face against you.
-So you've completely
given into it.
Will everyone who's
gifted suffer this fate?
If they do, the tragedy's
too much, Akifusa.
We've known each
other our whole lives.
I thought we were
family, or, maybe not.
Kanjosui Shooting Star!
Return Gyogen.
-So the blood and
tears were fake.
I should have known.
-You should have.
I'm a liar after all.
To think that I have to
kill you with my own hands.
I'm overwhelmed with sadness.
[theme music]
NARRATOR: Kana the Reader Model.
-Hey, Kana.
We saw it.
-Hey, I heard that Ienaga
was a reader model.
-For real?
-She's cute!
-And she's one of the top
three cutest in our grade!
IENAGA (VOICEOVER):
Oh, what am I gonna do?
I'm in the spotlight
all of sudden.
It's kind of embarrassing.
Don't let it bother you.
Blushing over it is stupid.
Just act naturally.
-Kana?
-Rikuo.
IENAGA (VOICEOVER):
Did he see it?
I wonder if he did.
Wait.
Am I blushing?
But I see him every day!
-Kana, there's no
club activities today,
so I'm heading on home.
You wanna go together?
-Oh.
Sure.
Did you see it?
Rikuo?
-Hm?
See what?
-Nothing.
IENAGA (VOICEOVER): Am I
relieved or disappointed?
-Where's Oikawa?
-I think she left already.
-I see.
NARRATOR: To be continued.
[theme music]
-How did things
turn out this way?
-I've not forgotten
that face of yours.
-I'd say that
makes you the liar.
-Recite the words
cleanse the evil.