[theme music]
[singing in Japanese]
-Who's there?
A Yokai?
-Oh.
Good.
It looks like I scared you.
You've lost if you've
shown fear to a Yokai.
The price of that is your eye.
-She's gone.
What the hell just happened?
I can't see things to my right.
That's because your eyeball
is in this world now.
-Don't you mess with me!
Shikigami Benkei's Naginata!
-Welcome to the
world of the dead.
Oh, my lady.
Just look.
It'll be your sixth liver.
And it's an onmyoji's too.
-It seems you have
even more promise
than your father,
daughter of Kiyokotsu.
-Lady Yura.
-What brought you back home?
Did something happen to you?
-Where's my stupid brother?
It took me forever getting
back here thanks to him.
-Huh?
-I mean, he could've
at least bought me
a ticket for the bullet train.
Doesn't he know that I
don't have any money?
Just thinking about
it makes me angry.
-Maybe it have something to
do with masters Koreto, Shuji,
and Gora.
-Is she our next leader?
-It's Yura.
I have just returned as ordered.
What's this?
Big brother, everyone's here.
-Oh, it's Yura.
-Grandpa, how have you been?
-Yura.
listen to me.
Starting now, your
new assignment
is to be a substitute
guardian of the Keicho Seal.
in the meantime, we'll
search for Hagoromo Gitsune's
current incarnation.
We'll use all of our
straight to ensure
that she's destroyed
once and for all.
-Who are you, lady?
-Again.
My mind wandered there.
-This is nice.
I wanna stay like
this and float away.
Are you worried
about your friend?
The one who went to Kyoto.
-Huh?
Yeah.
I guess.
RIKUO (VOICEOVER): Ms.
Keikain's older brother
said "they" finally
made their move.
He said it was Hagoromo Gitsune.
KIYOTSUGU: Hey!
Nura!
The guys back at your
house said you'd be here.
-Kiyotsugu.
-I heard that Yura
went home to Kyoto.
-Huh?
Yeah.
It seems so.
-So she left us to go home
to Kyoto for the summer, huh?
Boy, that Yura.
-She can't helpt it.
Her family's there.
-OK.
All of us are here now.
So what's up?
-Right.
Yura's in Kyoto.
And Kyoto's full of
history and Yokai.
And summer break means
independent study.
Let's go there.
To Kyoto!
-That really sounded rehearsed.
-I figured that
this would happen.
-You're always pushing
your plans on us.
-But ladies, summer break,
independent study, and Kyoto!
Don't tell me you're
passing up this opportunity!
You can't!
You will go, right?
[moaning]
-Hey, stop it.
I know you want to.
Isn't that right, Nura?
-Rikuo?
-Oh.
I-- uh-- I'll have
to ask grandpa first.
Well, see you.
-Ask him for what?
-Money to go?
-Well, well.
I finally found it.
-Grandpa?
-Rikuo, what do we need?
-Grandpa, I'm uh-- thinking
about going to Kyoto.
You know about Ms.
Keikain, right?
So--
-Do you have a
death wish, Rikuo?
-Huh?
Grandpa?
-Ha.
He's scared already.
You fool.
Can't even dodge
an old man's kick.
The Shikoku Yokai were nothing.
Even the flunkies over in
Kyoto could take you out.
-What the hell?
You damn geezer!
-Rikuo, if you insist
on going to Kyoto,
then draw your sword right now.
-Ahhh, that was nice.
Huh?
Master Rikuo, Supreme Commander,
what do you think you're doing?
-Here I come, Rikuo.
Will you be able to see me?
-You bastard.
-When two Ayakashi fight,
it is a competition of fear.
You'll get the edge
on that, and that's
when your total
victory is assured.
It is the first level
in an Ayakashi battle.
Nope.
Over here, Rikuo.
It looks like you can at
least learn by example.
But you can't just rely on that.
Seasoned Ayakashi would
go to the next level.
-Supreme Commander!
-If you went to Kyoto
now, you'd be helpless.
-Supreme Commander.
-We're done here.
-If I learn that trick,
can I go to Kyoto then?
-Why do you want to
go there so badly?
-Because there's someone
there I have to see.
She's there, right,
Hagoromo Gitsune?
Answer me, geezer!
-Aren't you being
too harsh on him?
Throwing your blade
against your own grandson--
You went overboard.
-That brat.
-Rikuo, you're better
off not knowing.
I couldn't bear it
if I lost you too.
No.
I think that I've been
too over-protective.
-Huh?
-Karasu Tengu, go
and call them all in.
-What was that?
You're sending
Master Rikuo there?
You can't!
They'll kill him.
GRANDPA: Quiet.
I don't want to here it.
KARASU TENGU: Supreme Commander!
-It's been a long
time, Lord Nurarihyon.
Are you certain?
There is a chance
that you may end up
losing your precious heir.
-That's fine.
Whatever it's going to take,
this is something he wants.
-He isn't up yet?
-It's been two days.
It could be that
he'll never wake up.
What'll be do then?
-By the way, the Kiyojuji
Paranormal Patrol was here.
They said they're going
to Kyoto in a week.
TSURARA: Focus on Master Rikuo.
And just what was the
Supreme Commander thinking?
Treating his own
grandson this way!
I mean, don't you
think it's too cruel?
-Hey, ladies.
Hide the master now.
-Why?
What's going?
-Just hurry.
We've got monsters on the way.
-Is there a weak child in here?
Is there a weak child in here?
-Sniff, sniff, Sniff.
It stinks of humans here.
-Sniff, sniff.
Whoa.
-He's the one.
-He's the one who smells
like a weak human.
-Let's take him home.
-Let him go!
-Stop trying to get in our
way, you naughty child!
-Hey, who are these guys?
-Master!
-Stop it.
The Supreme Commander
ordered this.
-Well then, it
looks like we'll be
holding onto your
grandson for a while.
We of the Oshu-Tono Clan.
TSURARA: Dear Master
Rikuo, how are you doing?
What a shock it must have been
to be taken away in your sleep
to some strange place.
But the Tohoku region is the
first place of many Yokai.
It's considered the homeland
of a wide variety of Ayakashi,
including my own ancestors.
Because of that, I believe
there's a thing or two
you can learn
there, Master Rikuo.
Please take good
care of yourself.
I've heard that
Tono is super cold,
and that its Yokai are super
cruel and super strong.
But I'll always be on
your side, Master Rikuo.
Hang in there.
-Hey, Tsurara.
I left the laundry over there.
-Huh?
You're awake.
-And there was some
talk of eating you,
if you didn't wake
up in an hour too.
-Huh?
-Is he really the heir to
the Nura Clan in Kanto?
-He's freaky.
His hair grew out right
after it turned dark.
-The rumors say that he's
got human blood in him.
He's only half Yokai.
-No.
Not even half.
I heard he's more like
a quarter Ayakashi.
-Yeah?
No wonder he's so weak.
-What the hell is this place?
-Finally awake, huh?
What a troublesome apprentice.
Go give Lord Akagappa
a proper greeting!
-So you're the grandson.
You look like him.
It's like his younger
self was reborn.
-What's that?
-He came here, and took all
our gifted Yokai with him.
And it weakened us.
I hate him.
You have a hateful face too.
-So who are you?
You know my old geezer?
And where am I?
-Hey!
You've shouldn't be so
cheeky with Lord Akagappa.
-Tono Village in
the Tohoku region,
this is an ancient
hidden village,
and the home of the Ayakashi.
Tono?
Hidden village?
-Hang in there and do your best.
All right.
Take him and put him to
work as an apprentice.
-Apprentice?
For Tohoku?
You're kidding, right?
I have to get to Kyoto
as soon as I can.
-To Kyoto?
Seriously?
-Nice one.
-Going there is like
death for someone who
can only bring fear,
-Oh?
Is that right?
He's trying to run!
-It's not that easy to escape.
Nice try though.
-A dog?
[laughter]
-A dog beat him.
-What a weakling.
The Nura Clan's next
head is less than a dog!
RIKUO (VOICEOVER):
It's like with Gramps.
What just happened?
What is this place?
-That hurt.
Oh great.
I just washed these.
-Hey, noobie!
I've got more laundry.
Make sure to wash it all.
Hey!
You haven't chopped
any firewood at all!
You're such hopeless child.
You can't even handle odd jobs!
-Hey.
What's the point of forcing
me to do this stuff?
What the hell am I here for?
-Your grandfather
sent you off to us,
and said the following--
it's fine if he dies.
Just train my fool
of a grandson for me.
-What?
He did?
-So get to work, noobie!
-Hey.
Hold on there.
Why do I have to walk so far
to hang all these clothes?
-Well not many spots in
this village get sunlight.
It's usually just Yokai aura.
RIKUO (VOICEOVER): That's right.
I'm still in my Yokai form.
-Don't slack off there, noobie!
-Damn it.
-Even the flunkies over in
Kyoto could take you out.
RIKUO (VOICEOVER):
That damn geezer.
What am I supposed to do here?
Doing laundry, huh?
It's kinda hard.
-Master Rikuo, just
bring it over here.
RIKUO (VOICEOVER):
Tsurara made it look easy.
All right.
I'm getting out of here.
Who needs this?
Besides, no one's watching.
A bridge.
Damn!
An illusion?
-Are you stupid?
You really don't know
about Tono Village, do you?
This is a hidden village.
You could say the
whole place is a Yokai.
Without the power
to cut through fear,
you're stuck here until you die.
RIKUO (VOICEOVER):
Cut through fear?
-Seasoned Ayakashi would
go to the next level.
-Hey, you.
-Itaku.
I'm a kamaitachi.
-What were you saying?
Cutting through fear.
The power to cut
through fear, huh?
That old geezer.
So that's why I'm
stuck in this village.
-Hurry on back and
do the laundry.
-Hey, kamaitachi.
Hold on a minute!
Wait!
Teach it to me.
What's that?
Hey.
What is all this?
-It's practice.
-Practice?
This?
They look serious.
-This is one of
our largest grounds
for combat training, a
special part of Tono.
Watch.
Don't let it
overwhelm you, stupid.
That was his fear.
It's really too much trouble
to put it into words.
When you bring out fear, it's
all about causing terrifying
by increasing everyone else's
awareness of your Yokai
presence.
-Right.
Yeah.
-But Ayakashi eventually
began fighting over territory,
and it then became necessary to
create ways to fight Ayakashi.
That proved to be
the next level.
RIKUO (VOICEOVER):
The next level?
-Who's this, Itaku?
Never seen him before.
-Oh.
It's him.
This is the boy that Itaku
got put in charge of training.
-Hey!
You spoiled it.
-I'm Amezo, a numakappa.
I hear you took over my
bathtub cleaning duties.
-And my firewood.
That's the hardest chore to do.
Awashima, the amanojaku.
-Heating bathwater
is a lot harder.
I'm Reira, the Yuki Onna.
She's Yukari, a zashiki-warashi.
-Cleaning and washing
are the basics.
Dohiko, the futachi.
-Nice to meet you.
-Likewise.
-You're from the Nura
Clan, aren't you?
-And he's Nurarihyon's
grandson too.
-Even so, he's got no
idea how do use fear.
-Really?
-And he's scared heir
to the Nura Clan?
-A Yokai who can't use fear?
-Was he spoiled?
-If it's just bringing
out fear, I can.
-Huh?
-Really?
You know how?
Show us.
-Sure.
-Whenever you're ready then.
-What's with that getup?
-He was just in pajamas,
so I let him borrow it.
-It's not bad.
-They say he took down
the Shikoku Yokai.
-The Shikoku?
I thought they were long gone.
RIKUO (VOICEOVER): OK.
So how exactly am I
supposed to bring fear?
-Just calm your mind.
I call this technique
Meikyo Shisui.
RIKUO (VOICEOVER):
-Gramps, Like this?
-He vanished.
-So this is a Nurarihyon's fear?
-No way.
He actually brought
fear to everybody here?
-Stay back.
I'm the only one who
will be fighting him.
If anybody's cutting
is fear, it'll be me.
[theme music]
Yura Keikain's Train Splash
BIG BROTHER (VOICEOVER): Sorry
I can't go back with you,
but here's something
to help you relax.
The next time you
drink Cola, you
should add peppermint
candy to it.
It'll blow you away,
and it'll help you grow.
-Big brother, he does
have a kind side.
Huh?
What the?
Is it a Yokai?
I'm so sorry.
I'll clean it up right away!
-She won't fall for that.
-Nope.
I just know that she'll try it.
-The end.
[theme music]
-You think you can
cause a scene here?
I'll kill you.
-And I'll take your head as a
gift to Lady Hagoromo Gitsune.
-Because I can't go to
Kyoto as a weakling.
-How interesting.