>> AND NOW ONLY ONE SEAL
REMAINS.
[ SINGING IN JAPANESE ]
>> WHOA!
>> THERE ARE SO MANY TORII
GATES HERE.
>> IT’S LIKE A TORII FOREST.
>> IT’S KIND OF CREEPY.
>> WE CAME TO THIS PLACE
JUST AS THAT YOKAI ADVISED US.
>> HEAD FOR FUSHIME INARI.
THAT IS WHERE THE FIRST SPIRAL
SEAL RESTS.
>> ARE YOU CERTAIN THAT WE CAN
TRUST HIM, MASTER?
>> GUYS LIKE HIM, THEY DON’T
REALLY FEEL LIKE THE LYING TYPE
TO ME.
>> THE SPIRAL SEAL.
IT’S OUR FIRST LEAD
TO HAGOROMO-GITSUNE.
>> I SUPPOSE SO.
>> LET’S CHECK THIS PLACE OUT.
>> THERE’S STILL A LOT OF
VISITORS HANGING AROUND HERE.
>> IT IS STILL DAYTIME,
AFTER ALL.
BUT EVEN SO, THEY CAN’T SEE
THE PILLARS OF YOKAI AURA
IN THE SAME WAY THAT
THEY CAN’T SEE US EITHER.
>> I’VE NEVER BEEN A WOMAN
DURING THE DAY BEFORE.
IT’S KIND OF HARD
TO MOVE AROUND.
>> HEY, WHERE DO YOU GO
WHEN NATURE CALLS?
>> HUH? THE MEN’S ROOM!
WHERE ELSE?
I’M A GUY! END OF STORY!
JUST LIKE RIKUO, RIGHT?
WAIT! ARE YOU HUMAN MOST OF THE
TIME OR A YOKAI? WELL?
>> I’M GLAD THAT TSURARA
ISN’T HERE TO SEE THIS.
>> THERE ARE SEVERAL ROUTES
FARTHER IN.
WE SHOULD SPLIT UP.
>> LET’S MEET UP THERE
AND BE CAREFUL.
>> OMOKARU-ISHI?
THAT’S A WEIRD NAME.
HEAVY! WHAT IS THIS?
>> WHAT’S WRONG, AWASHIMA?
>> IT’S NOTHING.
WHERE’S MY TEAM?
>> WE’RE OVER HERE.
>> OH, WITH RIKUO AND AMEZO.
>> HEY! WHAT DON’T YOU LIKE
ABOUT ME?
>> YOUR LOOKS.
>> REALLY?
>> A REPORT OF A GIANT SHIP
OF YOKAI?
>> YES. IT’S A RUMOR THAT
I’VE HEARD IN TOWN.
AND THEY SAY A NIGHT PARADE HAS
BEEN SAVING PEOPLE WHO WERE
TRYING TO LEAVE FUSHIME INARI.
>> IT’S MASTER RIKUO!
SEE? IT’S JUST LIKE I TOLD YOU.
HE’S HERE NOW.
>> YES, AND HEADED
TO FUSHIME INARI.
IT’S ALSO KNOWN
AS THE FOREST OF THE LOST.
A TROUBLESOME ONE NESTS THERE.
[ BOTH GASP ]
IF THEY ARE CAUGHT UP IN HIS
FEAR, THEIR NIGHT PARADE
WILL BE TORN TO SHREDS.
[ VOICES LAUGHING ]
>> AN OMOKARU-ISHI, HUH?
>> OH, SO YOU’VE HEARD OF THEM?
>> THEY SAY THAT IF IT FEELS
HEAVIER THAN YOU EXPECTED,
IT’S A SIGN OF BAD LUCK
OR SOMETHING LIKE THAT.
>> WAIT. REALLY?
HUH?
>> [ CRYING ]
>> HEY, WHAT’S WRONG?
YOU LOST?
SO ARE YOU HURT OR SOMETHING?
CRYING WON’T HELP.
COME ON! I’M IN A HURRY HERE!
>> [ CRYING ]
>> STOP CRYING, KID!
>> WHAT’S THE HOLDUP?
SHAKE A LEG.
>> WHAT THE...HEY!
HOLD ON A SEC!
DAMN IT! I CAN’T JUST LEAVE
THIS KID HERE.
>> I CAN’T WALK.
WILL YOU CARRY ME?
>> YOU’VE GOT TO BE KIDDING.
THIS IS THE REASON
WHY I CAN’T STAND KIDS!
HEY, WAIT UP!
WHAT?
HOLD ON!
WHERE’D THE OTHERS GO?
>> AWASHIMA?
>> HEY, THIS KID, THERE’S
SOMETHING WEIRD WITH HIM.
HEY, RIKUO.
>> THEY’VE ENTERED
THE THOUSAND TORII FOREST.
>> OH, MAN, HE’S GONE?
WHAT THE HECK?
IS THIS SOME KIND
OF JOKE, RIKUO?
RIKUO? AMEZO?
>> [ CRYING ]
>> DAMN IT!
WHERE DID THOSE GUYS GO?
WHO IS HE?
AN AYAKASHI?
AND WHAT’S WITH ALL THESE
TORII GATES HERE?
HMM.
HUH? WHO’S THERE?
WHAT? OW!
WHOA!
SOMEONE’S ARM?
WHAT IS THAT UP THERE?
MY LEG!
HEY, WAIT!
WHAT’S GOING ON HERE? WAIT!
AAH!
THAT WAS MY LEG!
QUIT IT ALREADY!
IT’S OUT.
IS IT THE KYOTO YOKAI?
I DON’T GET THIS.
BUT THERE’S A LOT OF THEM
COMING FROM THOSE GATES.
WELL, WHAT’S GOING ON HERE?
DON’T UNDERESTIMATE ME!
MY ARMS AND CLOTHES!
HOLD ON A SECOND HERE!
THAT’S THE ENEMY THERE?
WHAT THE HELL?
AAH!
IT’S NO USE.
WHAT IS THIS?
I DON’T EVEN KNOW
WHAT’S HAPPENING TO ME.
[ CRYING ]
AM I...AM I GOING TO DIE HERE?
>> WHAT’S THE MATTER?
I SEE THAT YOU’RE CRYING.
HA! THOUGH YOU ACT STRONG,
YOU’RE STILL A WOMAN.
>> THAT HAT! KUROTABO.
>> IT’S KUROTABO.
DO YOU RECALL THAT STONE?
UNFORTUNATELY, IT DIDN’T AFFECT
ME AS MUCH AS YOU, WHICH IS WHY
I DIDN’T GET DRAGGED INTO
THAT WORLD.
>> SO YOU TOUCHED IT, TOO?
>> THIS YOKAI SPIRITS PEOPLE
AWAY, UNDERSTAND?
IT USES THE STONE TO DRAW
FEARFUL PEOPLE INTO ITS OWN
WORLD.
>> I THOUGHT SO!
THEN I’D BETTER TRY TO FIND
YOU GUYS AS SOON AS I CAN.
>> I’M AFRAID IT’S YOU TWO
WHO ARE LOST.
>> [ GASP ]
KUROTABO!
>> AWASHIMA! YOU’LL HAVE TO CUT
THROUGH HIS FEAR ON YOUR OWN!
>> I AM THE GUARDIAN HERE,
KYOTO YOKAI SENJU-MUKADE
OF THE 27 FACES.
I WILL START
BY KILLING YOU FIRST.
>> KURATABO, WHAT WAS THAT?
I’M A WOMAN? THAT’S WHY?
I’M NOT CRYING BECAUSE OF THAT.
I’M AN AMANOJAKU.
IT’S ’CAUSE THIS IS SO MUCH FUN.
I GET TO SHOW MY FEAR TO THIS
DAMNED KYOTO AYAKASHI
RIGHT BEFORE I DESTROY HIM!
I TRAINED MY FEAR IN MY
HOMETOWN AND GET TO USE IT NOW.
I JUST CAN’T WAIT!
HERE GOES!
AWASHIMA THE MAIDEN
DANCES LIKE ANGELS IN HEAVEN.
DANCE OF THE BATTLE MAIDEN!
SINCE TIMES LONG PAST, WOMEN
HAVE DANCED BEFORE BATTLES
TO CALL FORTH VICTORY.
DID MY FEMININE FORM
BLOW YOU AWAY?
>> [ CRYING ]
>> HEY, YOU’RE STILL CRYING?
JEEZ.
WHAT? IT DIDN’T WORK?
>> [ CRYING ]
>> LADY, YOU THERE, YOU CANNOT
LEAVE THE FOREST OF THE LOST.
I AM THE GUARDIAN
OF THIS LEY-LINE.
>> WHAT? SLICING HIM IN HALF
DIDN’T WORK?
>> [ CRYING ]
WHERE’D YOU GO, MOMMY?
>> SHUT UP, KID!
WHAT’S GOING ON?
EVERY TIME HE CRIES,
THAT THING GETS STRONGER!
IS HE THE AYAKASHI?
MAYBE KILLING HIM IS THE ANSWER.
>> I’M AFRAID THAT IT’S YOU TWO
WHO ARE LOST.
>> SOME YOKAI CAN HAVE A
STRENGTH THAT’S UNBEATABLE WHEN
THEY’RE IN A SPECIFIC LOCATION.
>> SO WHAT,
THEY CAN’T LOSE THEN?
>> THEY CAN IF YOU FIND
THEIR SOURCE OF POWER.
YOU’VE GOT TO TAKE CARE
OF THAT FIRST.
OTHERWISE, ALL YOUR ATTACKS
WILL BE USELESS.
YOU’LL NEVER CUT THEIR FEAR.
>> HMM.
SINK OR SWIM.
I MIGHT AS WELL TRY IT.
>> [ CRYING ]
>> HEY, YOU JUST GONNA KEEP
CRYING LIKE THAT?
>> I’M SORRY.
>> IF SO, DO IT RIGHT HERE!
>> POSSESSION OF THE FEMALE
ANGEL, THE COMPLETE MATERNITY,
IZANAMI.
>> ARE YOU CERTAIN YOU SHOULD
BE TURNING YOUR BACK
TO YOUR ENEMY?
>> DON’T YOU WORRY.
I’LL PROTECT YOU.
YOU KNOW THAT I’LL SAVE YOU,
RIGHT?
>> MM-HMM...MOMMY.
>> STOP IT.
>> JUST LIKE I THOUGHT.
THIS PLACE IS REALLY JUST
A WORLD THAT HE CREATED.
YOU’RE A YOKAI WHO LIVES IN
THE WORLD MADE BY THIS KID’S
FRIGHTENED HEART AND YOU BECOME
STRONGER THE MORE HIS FEAR
GROWS.
SIT TIGHT.
I’M GONNA GET RID OF THIS YOKAI
RIGHT HERE AND NOW.
JUST YOU WATCH!
POSSESSION OF THE RAGING
DEMON, THE COMPLETE PATERNITY,
IZANAGI.
IN KOJIKI, AWASHIMA WAS
IZANAGI’S AND IZANAMI’S SECOND
CHILD, NOT MALE OR FEMALE.
THEY ABANDONED THE POOR KID.
THAT’S WHERE MY NAME COMES FROM.
I’M A DEMON AS A MAN,
AN ANGEL AS A WOMAN,
BECAUSE THAT’S WHAT
MY PARENTS WERE, TOO.
MY POSSESSION IS DOUBLE-EDGED.
>> HUH?
>> YOU’RE UNHURT, I TRUST?
>> WHAT THE...THERE YOU ARE!
>> IT SEEMS SO.
>> AWASHIMA, WHERE HAVE YOU
BEEN THIS WHOLE TIME?
>> THE CAN?
>> YEAH, RIGHT!
I WAS TAKING CARE OF A YOKAI!
>> HUH?
>> MASTER!
>> HEY, WHAT’S GOING ON?
>> IT APPEARS THAT SHE WAS MUCH
STRONGER THAN THE AYAKASHI
WHO NESTED THERE.
YOU HAVE GOOD VASSALS.
HOWEVER, YOU SHOULDN’T
CELEBRATE JUST YET.
SO YOU MUST BE HIS GRANDSON.
>> HEY, RIKUO,
WHO ARE THOSE GUYS?
>> ONMYOJI.
>> SERIOUSLY? ONMYOJI?
>> IT’S BEEN A WHILE,
YOKAI BRAT.
>> THE RESEMBLANCE IS UNCANNY.
IS YOUR GRANDPA DOING WELL?
>> WHO IS HE?
WHAT DO YOU WANT?
>> HE’S STILL ALIVE?
>> AYAKASHI THAT NESTS ABOVE
THIS LEY-LINE BECOME THE SEAL’S
CORNERSTONE TO ONCE AGAIN
PURGE THE AYAKASHI FROM KYOTO.
>> LOOK!
>> LADY HAGOROMO-GITSUNE!
>> DESTROY!
>> THE SKY IS CLEAR!
>> IS THIS A SEAL?
>> IT IS.
THERE WILL BE NO PEACE UNTIL
ALL EIGHT SEALS ARE IN PLACE.
I’M A SCION OF THE ASHIYA CLAN
AND 13th HEIR
OF THE KEIKAIN FAMILY.
CALL ME HIDEMOTO.
I AM PLEASED TO MEET YOU, TRULY.
>> HIDEMOTO?
>> GO SEE HIDEMOTO IF YOU CAN.
>> HIDEMOTO!
>> HUH?
>> HOW COULD YOU JUST
JUMP DOWN THERE?
WHAT DO I DO WITH THIS
SHIKIGAMI CARRIAGE?
[ PANTING ]
I’M BEAT HERE.
>> JUST SAY GO AWAY, YURA, DEAR.
DON’T DAWDLE NOW.
>> A SHIKIGAMI SHOULDN’T BE
TELLING ME WHAT TO DO!
>> YURA, HUH?
>> IT’S NURA.
>> HUH? OH, MASTER RIKUO!
IT’S BEEN SUCH A LONG TIME!
>> TSURARA!
>> HUH?
>> YOU’RE IN MY WAY!
OW! THAT HURT!
>> DON’T SPOIL OUR REUNION, YOU!
MEANY! YOU’RE JUST A WART.
>> WHAT’S GOING ON?
>> HEY, YOU’RE ONE TO TALK!
GO AWAY, YOU YOKAI!
>> YOU SAID GO AWAY.
>> AAH!
AAH!
>> WHOA!
>> NOT GOOD!
>> MASTER RIKUO!
>> YOU OKAY?
>> YES. DID YOUR TRAINING
IN TONO GO ALL RIGHT?
>> YEAH.
>> I WAS SO WORRIED ABOUT YOU,
BUT I KNEW YOU WOULD COME.
I HAD FAITH THAT YOU WOULD.
>> TSURARA?
>> OH, DON’T WORRY
ABOUT ALL YOUR FRIENDS.
THEY’RE SAFE AND SOUND.
AOTABO HAS BEEN GUARDING THEM.
>> [ SIGHS ] SO BORED.
>> OH, WHY CAN’T WE GO OUT
ANYWAY?
>> DON’T ASK ME.
>> OH, ALSO...
>> HUH?
>> HERE ARE MY LETTERS.
>> LETTERS?
>> I WANTED TO KEEP YOU UPDATED
ON EVERYTHING THAT’S HAPPENED
SINCE WE GOT HERE.
DEAR MASTER RIKUO, I’VE HEARD
IT’S VERY COLD IN TONO.
I KNOW YOU’RE IN TRAINING, BUT
PLEASE TAKE CARE OF YOURSELF.
DEAR MASTER RIKUO, I’M AT THE
KEIKAIN ESTATE NOW WITH THE
KIYOJUJI PARANORMAL PATROL
AND THAT OMNIYOGI GIRL.
MASTER RIKUO, KYOTO IS COVERED
BY OMINOUS CLOUDS AND JUST
OVERFLOWING WITH YOKAI AURA.
KUROMARU HAS GONE BACK
TO REPORT THIS.
>> YOU WROTE ALL OF THIS?
>> MM-HMM.
>> HEY, OVER HERE!
RIKUO? IS SHE THE ONE?
THE GIRL THAT YOU WANTED
TO COME SAVE?
>> THAT FRIEND OF YOURS
WHO’S SUPPOSED TO BE SUPER HOT?
>> HEY, INTRODUCE US!
>> NO, THAT’S HER.
>> YOU’RE REALLY HERE, NURA.
>> [ GROANS ]
>> HMM?
>> YOU’RE HEAVY.
>> REALLY?
>> HUH.
>> HEY, WHY’D YOU HAVE
TO THROW ME, YOU JACKASS?
>> HEY, YOU’D BETTER WATCH
YOUR LANGUAGE THERE, YURA.
>> [ LAUGHS ] SHE’S SILLY.
>> JERK!
>> IT WAS HIDEMOTO, RIGHT?
I’M GUESSING THAT YOU KNOW
MY GRANDFATHER.
IF YOU KNOW ABOUT OUR CURSE,
I WANT YOU TO TELL ME.
I’M HERE TO PUT AN END TO IT.
>> HIDEMOTO, THE 13th HEIR?
HE’S THE ONMYOJI PRODIGY
WHO FOUGHT HAGOROMO-GITSUNE
WITH US 400 YEARS AGO!
>> 400 YEARS?
>> I REMEMBER NOW.
THE SPIRAL SEAL, THE ULTIMATE
BARRIER THAT CONNECTED ALL THE
LEY-LINES TO KEEP YOKAI
OUT OF KYOTO.
THE SUPREME COMMANDER SAID
AYAKASHI WOULD HAVE TO BREAK
ALL THE SEALS TO GET INTO
THE CITY.
>> YES, THAT’S THE ULTIMATE
BARRIER I CREATED,
THOUGH IT’S DESTROYED NOW.
POWERFUL AYAKASHI WERE TURNED
INTO THE EIGHT PILLARS OF THE
SEAL AND THE KEIKAIN CLAN
GUARDED THEM.
YOU SPOKE OF BREAKING THE CURSE.
IF YOU INTEND TO CARRY ON
NURA’S WILL, PLEASE HEAR ME OUT.
I WANT YOU TO JOIN THE KEIKAIN
CLAN IN PUTTING EACH SEAL
BACK IN ITS PLACE.
TRUE, IT’S MY RESPONSIBILITY,
BUT I’M REGRETFULLY DEAD.
HAGOROMO-GITSUNE STANDS POISED
TO ENTER NIJO CASTLE
TO NEST AND GIVE BIRTH.
>> OH! GIVE BIRTH?
>> TO A CHILD?
>> SHE HAS UNDERGONE CENTURIES
OF REINCARNATION ALL FOR THIS
GOAL, TO BEAR HER CHILD,
THE EMBODIMENT OF EVIL.
YOU MUST ENSURE THE PILLARS
ARE SEALED ONCE AGAIN AND STOP
THE FLOW OF YOKAI AURA.
THEN USE HAGUN AND NENEKIRIMARU
TO DESTROY OUR FOE.
DO THIS.
>> YOU DON’T HAVE TO ASK ME
THAT.
THAT’S THE ONLY REASON
I CAME HERE.
>> I CAN’T WAIT!
I CAN’T WAIT!
I CAN’T WAIT TO FIGHT THEM!
IT LOOKS LIKE ALL THE STRONG
CHALLENGERS I WAS LOOKING FOR
ARE IN ONE SPOT!
[ SINGING IN JAPANESE ]
>> THIS TOOK PLACE WHEN RIKUO
JUST ENTERED JUNIOR HIGH.
>> HEY, SHE’S CUTE!
>> OH, THERE ARE LOTS
OF PRETTY FIRST YEARS.
>> SO HAVE WE DECIDED ON THIS
YEAR’S TOP THREE YET?
IT’S GONNA BE PRETTY TOUGH
FINDING THEM ALL.
>> LOOK OVER THERE!
>> WHOA!
>> WHAT? SHE’S SO CUTE!
>> WHO’S THE NERD?
>> THIS YEAR’S BATCH
IS TOTALLY FIRST-RATE!
>> SO WHO’S GONNA GO INTO
THE TOP THREE?
>> I DON’T KNOW.
>> TOP FOUR, THEN?
>> THAT MAKES IT EASIER.
>> LOOK BEHIND THE TELEPHONE
POLE!
>> SHE’S CUTE!
>> WOO-HOO!
>> WHAT ABOUT THE TOP FOUR?
>> SHUT UP!
WHO CARES ABOUT THAT?
DO YOU WANNA BE MY GIRLFRIEND?
>> DON’T TRY TO GET
THE JUMP ON US.
MOVE IT, FOUR EYES!
>> AAH!
>> HOW DARE YOU DO THAT TO...
>> MASTER RIKUO!
>> AND THAT’S HOW THE TOP FIVE
WERE CHOSEN! THE END!
[ SINGING IN JAPANESE ]
>> THIS IS MY NEW CASTLE.
>> A YOKAI WE MUST AVOID?
>> STAY BACK! I’LL FIGHT HIM.
>> JUST HANG ON!
I’LL EAT YOU HUNDRED DEMONS
SOON ENOUGH!