-What happened to Kyoto?
-This is crazy.
-What are those pillars
doing down there?
-What's going on?
-Uh?
-What the-- I'm not
turning into a man!
[yokai snickering]
-Hagoromo Gitsune.
[theme music]
KO-ONI: We're going to
crash right into the city!
TOFU: [whimpers]
NATTO: At this rate, all the
yokai who can't fly are goners!
-It's all on you, Treasure Ship.
Head for the mountain.
And try to slow down enough
to make an emergency landing!
-Huh?
It's so hard, but
I'll deal with it!
-Aarh!
KO-ONI: It can talk?
[ship groans]
-We made the turn!
-All right!
-Now, we just have to slow down.
-Don't cheer yet!
At this rate, the
hull's going to give!
[ship groans]
-[grunts]
-[cackling]
It won't be that easy!
-Oh, pain!
-[cackling]
-Damn him!
If he isn't stopped,
even if we slowed down,
the ship will still get wrecked!
[ship groans]
-This is too much!
[grunts]
[ship groans]
-[cackles]
You're going down!
-Possession!
The Wind Knife!
You shouldn't have stuck your
neck in front of my sickles!
Kyoto yokai make good prey.
They're stupid.
-What are you doing?
-[grunts]
KUBINASHI: You carved
a net out of tree bark!
[ship groans]
-Itaku!
-Shut up and don't let go!
NATTO: No!
We're slowing down,
but it's too late!
We're over the mountain!
TOFU: We're at the city!
-You've got to keep us
from crashing somehow,
Treasure Ship!
NATTO: He can't!
He passed out!
-[cackles]
They're dead meat.
Serves them right!
[laughing]
-Damn it all!
Is this it?
-[whimpers]
-At least, we'll die together!
-[sighs]
We're so close.
I can't die here.
-Why, thank you.
-Kyokotsu.
-What is it, my lady?
-A question.
If Kyoto became yours to rule,
then how would you remake it?
-Well, I think that Kyoto
is a very beautiful city.
I would destroy all of
the modern buildings
and just leave the
cultural ones around.
And too many humans live here.
I'd get rid of all
those worthless humans
and change the city
into a place for yokai.
A world like that would
definitely be a fun one.
-[giggles]
It certainly would.
Children are so honest.
-Thank you.
But I'm only repeating what
you taught me, my lady.
-Is that the case now?
The next seal is
where this all ends.
Our longstanding
wish will come true.
The ideal world for myself and
my child is nearly at hand.
-Huh!
Look over there!
-There's a river!
-It's Kamo River!
-Itaku, we'll set down there!
-I know that.
Don't give me orders!
[shrieks]
NATTO: All right!
TOFU: Uh!
I bit my tongue.
TE NO ME: Are we safe now?
KO-ONI: No, look ahead!
NATTO: NATTO: The
ship's going too fast!
We're going to crash!
Look!
ALL: We're not going to make it!
-[grunts]
-Fog!
[inaudible]
[cheers]
-[sighs]
-Pretty close call,
if you ask me.
-Who is that guy?
-Oh, right.
That was a great job, Shoei!
-Great.
If this is the beginning, we've
got some tough times ahead.
-Eeeh, wow, Kyoto's
nothing like I imagined!
-Yuki Onna and Aotabo are
already in the city, right?
-Why did those two have
to leave before us anyway?
-They came to act as
bodyguards since Master Rikuo's
schoolmates decided
to come to Kyoto, too.
KO-ONI: Oh, I wonder what
happened to that onmyoji girl.
Is she dead?
-A word, Master.
It's worse than we thought here.
We should rethink our plan.
Master Rikuo!
-One moment!
-What?
Hakuzozu?
-As you well know, I serve
Lady Hagoromo Gitsune.
Joining your side is
not an option for me.
However, I will
tell you one thing.
Head for Fushimi Inari.
That is where the first
spiral seal rests.
RIKUO (VOICEOVER): Spiral seal?
-Uh, that sounds
kind of familiar.
-And why should we do that?
Rikuo came here because
he's got a friend to save.
He's got no time for detours.
-This is no mere detour.
It is what you would call
a shortcut to whatever end
upon which you decide.
-A shortcut?
-Do as you please, whether
you believe me or not.
With that, I shall
take my leave.
I will say this to you, however,
you are no match for her!
-What?
-He's gone.
-So he's not going to join us?
-What was that about?
-Hm.
-Still, just looking
out at this city--
-I don't trust him.
-He may have had a point.
-Wh-- why don't we take a break?
KO-ONI: Yeah, we should.
Th-- this is a good spot.
-It sure is.
And the Treasure
Ship can fix itself.
-Huh?
It can do that?
-Plus, we've still
got good food here.
-He's right.
There's no rush.
KO-ONI: Yeah, yeah.
-Huh?
-[shrieks]
NATTO: It looks like the enemy
already knows we're here!
-Right.
-Yeah, um.
-Daah!
M-- Master Rikuo!
-No panicking.
[group gasping]
That's what the
enemy wants from us.
-Right!
-Hmm.
-We haven't been here
in quite a while.
Our first foot forward
has to be firm.
KARASU: How's the
Supreme Commander doing?
-I'd like to know that myself.
He's been like that
since receiving
word of Hagoromo
Gitsune's return.
KARASU: He must feel troubled.
I can't blame him.
-If the Kyoto yokai
stay the course,
their vengeance will undoubtedly
turn toward us someday.
Given that, we will have to
bolster our combat forces soon.
We should have stopped him.
Was it even necessary
for him to go to Kyoto?
Master Rikuo was
still in training.
Going there to save
a young onmyoji girl.
His human blood
must be to blame.
-Stop being so pessimistic.
Nothing's written in stone.
-But, Supreme Commander--
-Aren't you two curious to
see just how far Rikuo can go?
It's the first
time that he's ever
wanted to go take
someone down a notch.
We should all
respect his wishes.
-Honestly.
But wasn't it too soon?
Master Rikuo has a weakness--
the young master's human blood.
NARURIHYON: At my age, I
can't beat Hagoromo Gitsune.
But maybe Rikuo can.
-Wha--
-His human blood might not
be a weakness in this case.
At least, that's what
I've chosen to believe.
MAN: What's going on?
How could this happen?
You're saying that Kyoto has
been taken over by yokai?
That's what we're
supposed to tell people?
-Any faith that we had in
the Keikain Clan is gone now.
-You'll protect Nijo
Castle though, right?
What happened to that great
prodigy's seal you touted?
MAN: Prodigy?
Who are you referring to?
Could it be me that
you're speaking of?
-Huh?
-Everyone is doing their
best, I'll have you know.
But my seals are now at
their limit after 400 years.
-Your seals?
Just who are you?
-I am Hidemoto.
-Was that a joke?
-Hidemoto's right here.
-I wasn't finished.
I'm Hidemoto, the 13th Heir.
You see, Yura here summoned me
and brought me to this era--
well, as a shikigami anyway.
So I can only speak,
thanks to her power.
Right, Yura, my dear?
-That's fine and
everything, but why
are you still sticking around?
-That's really the 13th Heir?
-Yura summoned him?
So she really is gifted.
-All right, it looks
like everyone's here now.
-He's the best we've
ever had, right?
-You've heard all of the
legends, haven't y you?
-He sealed Hagoromo
Gitsune away 400 years ago.
So I'm sure that
he's got a plan.
-Ah!
Let me start with this first.
They're going to break the
last seal at Nijo Castle.
[crowd gasping]
HIDEMOTO: That vixen
is really quite strong.
And the followers who's
taken up her cause
are nothing to
gloss over either.
-My god!
-To be fair, yokai live
for thousands of years.
It's unthinkable that humans
could ever defeat them.
[laughs]
-What?
What was that?
-Just let them have that castle.
[chuckles]
However, they'll go on
the defensive from there.
Just like 400 years
ago, Hagoromo Gitsune
intends to give birth
there at Nijo Castle.
-To-- to give birth?
-Give birth to what exactly?
-Hm.
I'm not certain.
But I do have an inkling.
It will be something terrible
for both humans and ayakashi.
-Something terrible?
HIDEMOTO (VOICEOVER): The
being that Hagoromo Gitsune
will bear is their
longstanding wish.
As such, once she
takes the castle,
she'll need several weeks
to prepare for its birth.
That is our only
window for victory.
The Kyoto yokai have
united for that one wish.
If we can defeat their
mistress before the birth,
they will lose their
purpose and scatter.
Hagoromo Gitsune is
our greatest foe,
but she also happens to be
their greatest weakness.
-[gasps]
-So we'll wait until
then to make our move!
-I see, if we can carry
that out successfully.
-Two key things are
necessary for her defeat.
One is Hagun In other
words, Yura here.
-[gasping]
HIDEMOTO: You best hold
her in high esteem.
-So Yura is our clan's one hope?
-A girl who's only eaten tamago
kake gohan since coming back?
-And what does the food
I eat have to do with it?
-You should eat silky
eggs from now on.
-Well, someone's popular.
-But that's so expensive!
-Good for her.
And the second
thing that's needed
is a certain spirit blade.
It's called--
BOY: --Nenekirimaru.
-Uh!
That's correct.
What's this?
It would seem someone
has done his research.
-I'm the current
owner of that blade
as the grandson of Nurarihyon.
-Huh!
-His grandson?
Is that a fact now?
-I'll go visit the Nura Clan.
GIRL: That won't be necessary!
-[panting]
-What is this?
What's going on here?
-This city's a madhouse!
Ugh!
-Are you OK?
YOKAI: Let me eat your livers.
Give us your livers, humans!
-[gasping]
-[growls]
[both shriek]
YUKI ONNA: Master Rikuo
is on his way here.
-I know you.
-What the--
-Who is that girl?
-Who's this?
-Uh, she's a nobody!
Oh, don't listen
to her big brother!
What's the big idea?
Why did you come
here, Yuki Onna?
-I was out in the hallway
and overheard stuff.
-Just mentioning the fact that
I brought a yokai here could get
me kicked out!
-Yura, dear, who is she?
-Uh, no one special.
Honest!
-I'm one of the
Nura Clan's members.
-Shut up!
-The Nura Clan?
-You're coming with me!
Just a sec, big brother.
Nothing weird here.
[gasping]
-Wow!
-This should be enough
distance between us and them.
-Is this a storage room?
-No, this is my room!
-Yura, dear, this
girl is a yokai, now?
-Uhh.
-Excuse me.
Getting back to
what I was saying,
you want Master Rikuo
in Kyoto, right?
Don't worry.
He's finishing up the
rest of his training.
He'll come here as
soon as it's done.
-Yuki Onna.
Sorry, but his sword
is all we want.
-Well, that's not
necessarily true.
-Huh?
-We do need the
Nenekirimaru, of course.
But truthfully, the one
who defeated that fox then
was Nurarihyon.
-Uh.
-Would you happen to
be Setsura's daughter
or her granddaughter?
-Huh?
How'd you know?
She's my mother!
My name's Tsurara.
YURA (VOICEOVER):
What did he say?
-Now, then, about your leader.
You mentioned that
he was training.
Would you consider him strong?
Our foe's power grows
with every reincarnation.
Knowing that, do you
still believe he'll come?
-There was something
that I heard
Master Rikuo say one time.
-Huh?
-"Anyone who goes around trying
to hurt humans is going to have
to answer to me."
-Uh.
-Uhh.
-Master Rikuo's life is very
unusual, to say the least.
So he's made a lot of enemies.
But his beliefs are firm.
And he's always relied
on his own power
to forge his path in life.
That's why I'll always
believe in him, too.
-Well put, Tsurara, my dear.
If that's the kind
of fellow he is, then
I'll have to warn
him about the seals.
Yura dear, do you see it now?
-Uh?
-Those pillars of
hate haunt Kyoto.
They are the source
of the yokai's power.
Step into them blindly and
you'll lose your footing.
[yokai snickering]
-What the heck?
It's the middle of
the day right now.
-It sure is.
But the place is crawling
with Kyoto yokai.
-Don't let them get to you.
Did you already forget
what the master just said?
-That's right.
And you're part of his Night
Parade of 100 Demons as well.
KEJORO (VOICEOVER):
Master Rikuo, I died.
You thought I still
had to protect
the master I served in life.
But you, you made
me feel needed.
You became my new master.
And so for you--
-Kurotabo, the
Assassin Monk has come.
So run while you can.
-Move it, asinine monk!
-Yeah!
-Hey!
It's the Assassin Monk!
-Heeh, yaah!
Haah!
-Yeah!
-Haah!
[grunts]
-Yaah!
-Those Tono guys.
-Kuro, they may not
have exchanged cups,
but still, they're allies
Master can rely on.
We should go, too.
-Agreed!
-You know, it's funny.
I just don't feel
like I can lose.
As long as I have you
with me, my 100 Demons.
Let's get this show on the road.
It's time for our
Night Parade to break
that fox's 400-year curse!
NIGHT PARADE: Yeah!
[music playing]
MALE YOKAI: So
they're the Nura Clan?
-They are.
-Don't interfere, Kidomaru.
Every single one
of them is my prey.
And I won't to be sharing
them with that old fox.
[music playing]