[ LAUGHING ]
>> THAT CHILD BELONGS TO US.
>> I WANT TO TALK
TO THE HUMAN PART OF YOU
TO CLEAR UP
MY IMPOSSIBLE MEMORY.
>> WHAT IS NURA TALKING ABOUT?
THE HUMAN HAGOROMO-GITSUNE?
>> THEY SAY YOU’VE BEEN
REBORN MANY TIMES
IN HUMAN BODIES.
[ GRUNTS ]
>> BE CAREFUL!
[ GROANS ]
>> HAGOROMO-GITSUNE
MAY NOT REMEMBER MY FATHER,
BUT YOU’RE NOT THE ONE
THAT I’M ASKING.
I WANT THE HUMAN PART OF YOU!
>> THAT PART DOES NOT EXIST!
>> IT’S DEFINITELY FUZZY,
BUT THERE’S THIS MEMORY
THAT I HAVE.
I REMEMBER SEEING YOU
LONG AGO BACK HOME
IN THE FALLING PETALS.
>> THAT MEMORY AGAIN.
>> IT WAS YOU, RIGHT?
>> SILENCE!
IT WASN’T ME.
SUCH PRATTLE MEANS NOTHING
TO ONE WHO HAS BEEN REBORN
FOR A THOUSAND YEARS.
THE MEMORIES HELD IN
THIS HOST BODY ARE GONE.
>> WHAT DO YOU MEAN,
YOU RECOGNIZE HER FACE?
>> I MEANT EXACTLY
THAT, KAPPA.
SOMEONE’S BEHIND
THIS INCARNATION OF HERS
AND PULLING ALL THE STRINGS.
>> WHAT?
>> SO THIS IS WHERE
YOU’VE BEEN, SUPREME COMMANDER?
>> OH, YOU FINALLY MADE IT.
>> OR MORE ACCURATELY,
YOU RUSHED OFF WITHOUT US.
>> LET’S GO, GUYS.
WE’RE DRAWING
THE CURTAIN ON THIS ACT.
>> I DIDN’T GET WHAT YOU
JUST SAID, OLD MAN!
>> OH, DIDN’T YOU HEAR ME?
THAT CHILD NUE BELONGS TO US.
>> YOU’RE TELLING ME
THAT NUE BELONGS TO YOU GUYS?
>> THAT’S RIGHT,
THOUGH I SUPPOSE
I SHOULDN’T HAVE SAID US
IF I WANTED TO BE PRECISE.
I’M JUST A SMALL PIECE OF HIM.
>> I CAN’T SAY THAT
I’M REALLY FOLLOWING YOU.
YOU’RE NOT MAKING
ANY SENSE AT ALL.
[ LAUGHS ]
>> I DOUBT THAT A FOOL
WHO WAS TRICKED BY AN ONMYOJI
INTO A 400-YEAR SLUMBER
COULD EVER GRASP
WHAT I’M SAYING.
>> OH, IS THAT RIGHT?
YOU’VE GOT A WEAPON RAISED
IN FRONT OF ME, YOU KNOW.
YOU WANT TO FIGHT, DON’T YOU?
>> HMM.
>> WHAT IS GOING ON?
WHAT DID YOU JUST DO TO ME?
HMM?
>> WHEN IT COMES
TO FULFILLING OUR GOAL,
WE WILL TAKE NO CHANCES
AND THAT INCLUDES YOU,
TSUCHI-GUMO.
[ LAUGHS ]
[ GRUNTS ]
>> QUIT GETTING IN MY WAY,
YOU ANNOYING BUGS!
>> ITAKU!
GO ON WITHOUT US!
>> WHAT?
[ CHUCKLES ]
>> I SEE.
SO IT’S NOT ENOUGH.
THERE’S NOT ENOUGH
BLOOD HERE FOR YOU.
[ GRUNTS ]
THAT’S WHAT YOU’RE SAYING,
RIGHT, DAD?
[ GRUNTING ]
>> I CAN’T GET
THESE THINGS OFF ME!
[ GIGGLES ]
>> YOU LITTLE BRAT!
>> HOLD STILL NOW.
YOUR EYES ARE MINE.
[ LAUGHS ]
>> SHOEI? ARE YOU ALL RIGHT?
>> I’LL BE FINE,
SO GET GOING.
>> YOU DID A GOOD JOB
HANGING IN THERE.
>> OW!
[ GASPS ]
>> GO!
>> WHAT THE...?
ARE YOU WITH THE NURA CLAN?
>> I EXCHANGED CUPS OF
LOYALTY WITH MASTER RIKUO.
>> GOTCHA.
I DON’T REALLY KNOW YOU,
BUT IT LOOKS LIKE OWE YOU ONE.
>> ALL RIGHT.
LEAVE THE BIG GUYS TO ME.
HEH.
>> I’M GOING TO MAKE SURE
THAT YOU BECOME
THE LORD OF PANDEMONIUM,
MASTER RIKUO.
>> WE GOTTA STOP THOSE GUYS!
>> DON’T LET THEM NEAR LORD NUE!
>> PROTECT LADY
HAGOROMO-GITSUNE!
>> DAMN IT!
THEY NOTICED WHAT
WE WERE UP TO!
>> JUST KEEP MOVING.
ARE THOSE LITTLE YOKAI
YOU’VE GOT SLOWING YOU DOWN?
>> LIKE I COULD HELP IT!
THESE GUYS SAID THEY WANTED
TO TAG ALONG, NO MATTER WHAT.
I COULDN’T LEAVE ’EM!
>> HURRY UP AND CLIMB,
YOU IDIOT!
>> I SWEAR, THAT RIKUO
SURE IS A POPULAR GUY.
>> WHAT ARE WE SUPPOSED
TO DO NOW?
DON’T YOU HAVE A TRUMP CARD,
13th HEIR?
THIS WAS YOUR SEAL.
>> I’M AFRAID I HAVE
NOTHING OF THE SORT.
>> HEH!
SO IT’S UP TO THE HUMANS
LIVING NOW TO DEAL WITH
ALL THE CONSEQUENCES.
WELL, THAT’S FAIR.
IT’S NOT LIKE WE CAN KEEP
DEPENDING ON THE DEAD.
THE REST IS UP TO US NOW.
>> THIS WILL ULTIMATELY
BE A FUTILE STRUGGLE
UNLESS WE CAN KEEP HER STILL
AND GET THE EXORCIST
BLADE NENEKIRIMARU IN RANGE.
SO WE CANNOT ALLOW NURARIHYON’S
GRANDSON TO BATTLE ALONE.
IT IS CRUCIAL WE COOPERATE.
>> I KNOW.
>> I’M GLAD TO HEAR THAT.
BUT THIS HAGOROMO-GITSUNE
IS MORE POWERFUL AND FIGHTS
DIFFERENTLY THAN THE ONE
I ONCE KNEW.
SHE MAY WELL BE INVINCIBLE NOW.
>> I’LL HAVE YOU KNOW
WE HAVEN’T JUST BEEN
SITTING ON OUR HANDS
THIS WHOLE TIME.
>> REALLY?
I RELISH THE THOUGHT OF THAT.
[ GRUNTING ]
>> I HAVE TO HELP HIM.
>> IS SOMETHING WRONG?
YOU’RE LOSING STRENGTH
BEFORE MY VERY EYES.
TIGER KILLER!
[ GROANS ]
>> VERMIN.
STAY SILENT NOW.
>> MASTER RIKUO!
>> MASTER!
>> YOU CAN’T LET
HER BEAT YOU, RIKUO!
>> IMMOBILIZED, YOU CANNOT
BRING FORTH YOUR FEAR.
TIME TO END THIS.
[ LAUGHS ]
[ GASPS ]
>> WHO ARE YOU, LADY?
>> WHAT IS THIS?
>> BANISH INTO THE ABYSS!
YURA MAX!
[ GASPS ]
>> NURA!
GET OUT OF HERE RIGHT NOW!
>> YURA?
>> I SEE.
THE HAGUN USER.
[ GASPS ]
>> YURA, WHAT ARE YOU DOING?
MOVE IT!
>> NO...
[ GRUNTS ]
>> PROTECT YURA,
PROTECT YURA!
[ GASPS ]
>> MAMIRU?
>> I KNOW, RYUJI.
THIS TASK IS MY TOP PRIORITY.
>> MAMIRU?
>> STAND BACK, YURA.
I’LL PROTECT YOU.
AFTER ALL, IT IS
FOR THIS REASON THAT I CHANGED.
IT WAS AN ORDER
TO PROTECT YURA
THAT I BECAME THIS WAY.
MAMIRU...
THE IMPORTANCE OF HAGUN
IS SOMETHING WE’RE ALL AWARE OF.
I CAN’T PROTECT YURA,
SO MAKE SURE YOU DO,
NO MATTER WHAT, MAMIRU.
>> THE WIELDERS OF NENEKIRIMARU
AND HAGUN NOW STAND
BEFORE HAGOROMO-GITSUNE.
[ GROWLS ]
[ SHOUTS ]
>> LORD IBARAKI-DOJI!
[ GROWLS ]
>> I’M GONNA CHOP
YOU BOTH TO PIECES!
[ GROWLS ]
[ GRUNTS ]
>> YOU’RE FINISHED!
[ WAILING ]
>> HE’S FAST!
WHAT THE HELL?
[ GASPS ]
[ GIGGLES ]
>> HUH?
THERE WERE TWO OF THEM!
WHERE DID THE OTHER ONE GO?
>> HEY!
>> GET THAT GUY!
>> OKAY!
[ GRUNTING ]
[ WAILING ]
>> WHY, YOU!
[ GRUNTS ]
>> MY LADY!
>> HUH, IBARAKI-DOJI
AND KYOKOTSU WERE USELESS
IN THE VERY END.
[ SCREAM ]
>> HUH?
>> OH, MY CHILD.
OH, MY CHILD!
IS THAT YOU?
>> THE SHELL IS BREAKING OPEN!
>> NUE!
>> MY SON!
MY SON!
I HAVE WAITED SO LONG!
>> NO WAY!
>> WE DIDN’T MAKE IT.
IT’S TOO LATE!
>> NOT YET.
I’M NOT DONE TALKING TO YOU,
SO GET BACK HERE.
>> THE SIDESHOW IS OVER.
THAT SO-CALLED BATTLE
OF OURS WAS NOTHING MORE
THAN A GRAND EXHIBITION
ON THE EVE OF
MY DEAR CHILD’S BIRTH.
HOW IT LINGERED.
THOSE THOUSAND YEARS
ARE COMING BACK TO ME.
>> HUH?
>> WHAT IS THIS?
>> A VISION FROM THE PAST?
>> THESE ARE LADY
HAGOROMO-GITSUNE’S...
>> HER MEMORIES
ARE BEING REFLECTED
ON THE FRAGMENTS
OF NUE’S SHELL?
>> MY CHILD WAS CONSTANTLY
IN MY THOUGHTS
THROUGH EVERY REBIRTH.
EACH TIME, MY WISHES
HAVE BEEN DASHED
AND WHEN I THOUGHT I HAD
THE POWER 400 YEARS AGO...
IF YOUR CLAN
HAD NOT INTERFERED,
I WOULD HAVE SEEN
MY CHILD AGAIN MUCH SOONER!
[ GROANS ]
>> THIS TIME, IT TRULY
WILL BE THE END.
>> OLD MAN...
[ GASPS ]
>> WHAT?
THAT MEMORY THERE...
>> THE SECOND HEIR?
>> LOOK!
MASTER RIHAN, HE’S IMPALED!
>> IS THAT
MASTER RIKUO’S MEMORY?
>> AGAIN!
[ GROANING ]
WHAT ARE YOU PLOTTING
TO DO THERE, LITTLE GIRL?
>> CRAWL, GENGEN, RIGHT NOW!
>> YURA, I’LL PROTECT YOU.
[ GROANS ]
[ GRUNTS ]
>> YURA, DESTROY HER!
>> SHIKIGAMI HAGUN!
HA!
[ GROANS ]
>> HAGUN, GO NOW!
[ SHOUTS ]
[ GASPS ]
[ GROANS ]
>> FATHER?
[ HEART BEAT ]
WHY’D YOU SAY THAT?
WHAT’S GOING ON HERE?
>> WHY?
WHY IS THIS HAPPENING?
IT’S INCONCEIVABLE!
THAT HOST WAS PURPORTED
TO BE THE PERFECT ONE!
WHAT INJUSTICE IS THIS?
MY HEAD FEELS FIT TO BURST!
OH!
WHY?
I WAITED 400 YEARS
AND YOU SAID
THIS WAS THE PERFECT VESSEL!
MINAGOROSHI-JIZO!
IT WAS YOU.
WHAT MISCHIEF DID YOU PLAY
WHEN YOU RESURRECTED ME?
[ LAUGHS ]
>> WHO ARE YOU, LADY?
[ GASPS ]
>> YOU’VE DONE WELL.
WITH THIS, MY LONGSTANDING WISH
HAS BEEN REVIVED.
>> AND WHO’S
THAT OTHER PERSON THERE?
WHO IS THE ONE
WHO KILLED MY DAD?
TELL ME.
>> NO!
SEIMEI, WERE YOU
THE ORCHESTRATOR
OF THIS TRAVESTY?
I DEMAND ANSWERS!
SEIMEI!
I’M FADING!
THE PAIN FEELS LIKE FIRE!
ANSWER ME, SEIMEI!
ANSWER ME!
>> MOTHER, FORGIVE ME.
[ GROANING ]
>> OH, SEIMEI,
HAS YOUR DESIRE
AT LAST BEEN FULFILLED?
>> I’M SORRY.
ALTHOUGH I WAS IN HELL
AT THE TIME,
I WAS INDEED THE ONE
WHO SENT YOU THE CHILD.
I DIDN’T FORESEE
THOSE HARDSHIPS.
>> I SEE, BUT YOU’VE
EXPLAINED ENOUGH.
ALL IS FORGIVEN.
SO COME CLOSER.
MY SEIMEI.
AT LONG LAST, YOU’RE IN MY ARMS.
>> THAT’S HELL YOU SEE THERE.
>> HELL, SEIMEI?
>> I WAS THERE
A THOUSAND YEARS,
THE PLACE ALL AYAKASHI
AND HUMANS RETURN TO.
[ GROANS ]
>> SEI--
>> I THANK YOU, MY DEAR MOTHER,
FOR THOSE THOUSAND YEARS.
BECAUSE OF YOU,
I CAN WALK THIS PATH ONCE MORE.
THROUGH THOSE LONG YEARS,
YOU WERE MY SUN,
MY LIGHT OF HOPE
AND MY WARMTH.
>> WHY, SEIMEI?
SEIMEI!
>> IT IS BY TURNING
MY BACK ON YOU
THAT I CAN WALK THIS PATH.
>> SEIMEI!
I LOVE YOU!
>> WITH LIGHT BEHIND YOU,
DARKNESS CASTS ITS SHADOW.
I’LL PROCEED AS THE NIGHT PARADE
OF A HUNDRED DEMONS TRUE LORD.
COME ALONG NOW,
MY AYAKASHI BRETHREN,
WITH ME.
>> HE’S BACK!
AT LONG LAST!
>> IT’S NUE!
>> ABE NO SEIMEI!
[ LAUGHING ]
>> THE BIRTH OF
THE LEGENDARY MASTER
HAS TAKEN PLACE!
[ LAUGHS ]
MAY LORD NUE REIGN FOR ETERNITY!
>> ALL ALONG, IT WAS YOU!
[ LAUGHS ]
>> HUH?
>> SEIMEI!
YEAH!
IT’S BEEN A THOUSAND YEARS!
>> SO YOU’RE RIHAN’S
REAL SON?
>> NURA WILL GET
HIMSELF DESTROYED!
>> IT’S LIKE YOU COULD
ALMOST BE OUR DAUGHTER.
>> NO! MASTER RIHAN!