>> SOKOKUJI TEMPLE.
>> IF SHE’S A SACRIFICE,
PRESENT HER TO OUR LADY,
NOT THAT YOU’LL LISTEN TO ME.
I CAN’T BELIEVE
YOU ONLY TOOK ONE.
WE DON’T HAVE TIME
TO WASTE ON THIS.
>> I’M JUST WAITING
FOR THE REAL FUN TO BEGIN.
>> WAITING FOR THE REAL FUN?
[ LAUGHS ]
I SHOULD HAVE KNOWN.
FOCUS ON OUR GOAL,
THE TASK WE LEFT
UNFINISHED CENTURIES AGO,
THE BIRTH OF THE ONE NUE.
>> NUE? NUE, HUH?
>> I SEE.
>> THAT REMINDS ME.
I WAS WONDERING ABOUT SOMETHING.
WHERE’D THE TENGU
FROM MOUNT KURAMA GO?
AND WHO WAS THAT OLD MAN
WITH THE CREEPY EYEBALL?
I SUPPOSE THAT TENGU
PROBABLY DIED OF OLD AGE
WHILE I WAS GONE.
>> TENGU?
WHAT ARE YOU TALKING ABOUT?
>> HUH?
>> IT’S BEEN A LONG TIME.
YES, THIS IS IT.
EVERYTHING’S GOING
ACCORDING TO PLAN.
[ CACKLING ]
THAT WAS EXCELLENT WORK.
>> DIE.
>> KUBINASHI!
WHAT ARE YOU DOING, KUBINASHI?
HAVE YOU LOST IT?
>> HEY! DON’T BUTT IN!
HEY, QUIT IT!
THAT HURT!
>> OF COURSE, I’M GOING
TO BUTT IN.
YOU’D BE DEAD NOW
IF I HADN’T INTERFERED!
QUIT TRYING TO ACT TOUGH!
THERE’S NO WAY YOU CAN
BEAT THEM ALL ON YOUR OWN.
>> LEAVE ME ALONE.
THIS SUITS ME JUST FINE.
I’LL HANDLE
THE KYOTO YOKAI MY OWN WAY.
I CAN DO THIS ALONE.
>> I NEVER REALIZED
THAT YOU WERE THIS STUPID,
AND IMMATURE!
YOU DON’T HAVE
TO FIGHT ON YOUR OWN.
WE CAN WORK TOGETHER
JUST LIKE IN THE OLD DAYS.
YOU’RE ON OFFENSE.
DEFENSE WAS ALWAYS MINE, RIGHT?
SO STOP TRYING TO BEAR
THESE BURDENS ALONE.
WE’RE PARTNERS.
LET’S DO THIS, KUBINASHI!
COME AND GET US, DEMONS!
YOU’LL LOSE YOUR HEADS
JUST LIKE THIS GUY OVER HERE!
[ GRUNTING ]
>> I WON’T FAIL AGAIN!
YOU WON’T GET PAST ME!
[ RUMBLING ]
>> A BLACKOUT!
>> WHAT’S GOING ON?
>> THIS IS AN OLD BUILDING!
THE WHOLE PLACE IS A DEATH TRAP!
>> I DON’T WANNA SEE YOKAI!
AND I SURE AS HECK DON’T WANNA
GET CRUSHED IN AN EARTHQUAKE!
DO YOU HEAR ME?
>> COME ON, GUYS.
WOULD YOU PIPE DOWN?
I’M TRYING TO SLEEP HERE.
WHAT’S WITH YOU?
>> KURATA.
>> YOU WERE SLEEPING?
[ CRASHING ]
>> I’M HITTING THE HEAD.
>> HUH?
>> HEY, KURATA, HOLD IT.
YOU CAN’T GO NOW.
IT’S NOT SAFE.
>> ARE YOU THAT WORRIED
ABOUT ME?
HMM!
HEY, MOVE IT!
>> HUH? WHAT?
>> AOTABO, I WANT YOU
TO STAY BEHIND AND GUARD THEM.
>> HEY, HOLD ON THERE!
WHY ME?
>> WHAT ARE YOU TALKING ABOUT?
WEREN’T YOU ONCE A YOKAI
WHO PROTECTED CHILDREN?
THAT MAKES YOU THE PERFECT
PERSON FOR THIS JOB.
>> THAT’S NOT HOW
I WOULD PUT IT.
>> MR. MONK!
[ CHILDREN LAUGHING ]
>> COME BACK SOON, MR. MONK.
[ GRUNTS ]
>> I’M CERTAIN THAT
OUR MOTHER OF DARKNESS
WILL RELISH EATING YOUR LIVER.
>> DAMN IT!
>> HEY, WHAT THE HELL
ARE YOU UP TO?
YOU GUYS AREN’T SUPPOSED
TO BE HERE.
>> AND WHO WOULD YOU BE?
>> THE HUMAN AND AYAKASHI
WORLDS OUGHT TO STAY SEPARATE.
AND I’VE GOTTA SAY I’M NOT
FOND OF THIS, NEEDLESSLY
TAKING LIVES, I MEAN.
>> AREN’T YOU
A FELLOW YOKAI YOURSELF?
WHAT ARE YOU SPOUTING?
>> I DON’T CARE WHO YOU ARE!
OUT OF THE WAY!
>> THOUGH IT’S A DIFFERENT STORY
WHEN IT COMES TO SCUMBAGS
LIKE YOU GUYS.
SORRY, PAL, BUT IT’S TIME
YOU HIT THE ROAD.
I DON’T OWE THE ONMYOJI A THING.
BUT THERE ARE SOME PEOPLE
I’VE GOT TO PROTECT.
>> OH?
>> KUBINASHI, LET’S DO IT!
[ GROWLING ]
>> KEJORO’S FEAR,
DISHEVELED HAIR.
DANCE OF THE COURTESAN!
IS SOMETHING THE MATTER?
YOU DEMONS ARE SO PITIFUL.
WE’LL BE SENDING EACH
AND EVERY ONE OF YOU TO HELL.
>> GET IT TOGETHER, GUYS.
THEY’RE KILLING YOU.
>> SEE? IT’S BETTER THIS WAY.
I’VE GOT YOUR BACK LIKE
NO ONE ELSE, SO YOU CAN
FOCUS ON ATTACKING HEAD-ON.
ALONE, WE’RE WEAK.
>> I HEARD SOMETHING LIKE
THAT A LONG TIME AGO FROM HIM.
>> YOU AND YOUR FRIENDS WERE
TORTURED TO DEATH BY YOKAI,
SO YOU BECAME ONE TO GET REVENGE
AND THAT’S WHY YOU’VE BEEN
GOING AROUND KILLING YOKAI.
I CAN SEE THAT YOU’RE STRONG,
BUT DON’T YOU THINK
YOU’VE DONE ENOUGH?
>> I’VE NEVER SEEN
FEAR LIKE YOURS.
WHAT WAS THAT?
>> YOU COULD CALL IT
A SECRET TECHNIQUE.
ONLY THE LEADER
OF A NIGHT PARADE
CAN USE FEAR LIKE THAT.
STILL, PEOPLE ARE STRONGER
WITH FRIENDS, DON’T YOU THINK?
>> STRONGER?
ALL THEY EVER DO
IS GET IN THE WAY.
IF THEY NEED PROTECTION,
THEY’RE DEAD WEIGHT.
I DON’T WANT THAT OR
THE HOPELESSNESS YOU FEEL
WHEN YOU LOSE ONE.
I’M GONNA KILL YOUR FRIENDS
AND ALL BY MYSELF, TOO!
>> NOT TODAY.
>> WAIT!
PLEASE, SIR!
I BEG OF YOU,
TAKE MY LIFE IN HIS PLACE!
I OFFER IT FREELY,
SO PLEASE SPARE HIM!
>> STAY OUT OF THIS, KINO!
GET LOST!
>> WHAT DO YOU KNOW?
LOOKS LIKE YOU DO HAVE SOMEONE
WHO WANTS TO PROTECT YOU.
LISTEN, KUBINASHI.
WHEN YOU RISKED YOUR OWN LIFE
FOR SOMETHING IMPORTANT TO YOU
LIKE THIS LADY HERE JUST DID,
THAT’S TRUE STRENGTH.
YOUR STRENGTH IS
A SHAM, KUBINASHI.
ANYBODY CAN GO AROUND
FIGHTING ALL BY THEMSELVES
WITHOUT A CARE
IN THE WORLD, BUT US?
WE FIGHT TO PROTECT THINGS
THAT ARE IMPORTANT TO US.
DON’T YOU THINK THAT
OUR WAY IS CLASSIER?
>> THIS IS LIKE BACK THEN.
I EXCHANGED CUPS OF LOYALTY
WITH HIM AND LEARNED
THE TRUE MEANING OF THOSE WORDS.
>> WHETHER YOU FIND MY HAIR
BEAUTIFUL OR TERRIFYING,
IF YOU SHOW ANY FEAR,
I GUARANTEE YOU WON’T
GET PAST ME.
>> HEY, ARE YOU GUYS
DEMONS OR WHAT?
QUIT LETTING HER DISTRACT YOU.
JUST CUT HER HAIR.
DEVIL’S DRUMSTICKS,
CHOPPING SCISSORS!
[ GASPS ]
>> THERE, THAT’S BETTER.
>>GOTCHA.
>>WHAT?
WHAT’S THIS PATTERN?
>> DEATH TENDRILS.
SPIRAL BLADE!
YOU WERE RIGHT.
IT SEEMS I REALLY AM A WEAK
AND UNWORTHY YOKAI.
AND YOU HELPED ME REALIZE
THAT FACT AGAIN.
THANK YOU, KINO.
>> IDIOT!
>> YOU’RE STILL GREEN,
A COUNTRY BUMPKIN
WHO DOESN’T KNOW A THING.
FROM NOW ON, YOU SHALL
BE KNOWN AS AOTABO.
THOSE FISTS OF YOURS CAN BREAK
STONES AND THOSE LARGE PALMS
CAN COMPLETELY CRUSH
A HUMAN SKULL WITH EASE.
YOU’RE A FOOLISH APOSTATE MONK
WHO HAS KILLED
A THOUSAND WARRIORS.
IF YOU CONTINUE TO KILL,
YOU WILL TURN INTO
A MONSTER LIKE THE SHOMEN-KONGO.
SAVE PEOPLE UNTIL THAT AMOUNT
IS EQUAL TO THE NUMBER
OF YOUR SINS.
CHOOSE TO REGAIN YOUR HUMANITY
OR BECOME A DEMON.
>> SOME PEOPLE
THAT YOU MUST PROTECT?
IT WOULD APPEAR THAT YOU DON’T
BELIEVE IN OUR GREAT CAUSE.
YOU’RE A FOOL TURNING
HIS BACK ON GOD.
>> HEY, PRETTY BOY!
QUIT ALL YOUR BABBLING
AND GET OUT OF HERE.
>> YOU LACK RESPECT
WHEN ADDRESSING OTHERS.
YOU’RE JUST LIKE IBARAKI-DOJI.
FOOLISH YOKAI, YOU SHALL
REPENT FOR THIS AFFRONT!
[ GROWLING ]
>> YOU’LL MAKE ME REPENT?
WHAT DOES THAT WORD MEAN?
SORRY TO BREAK THIS TO YOU,
I’M A BUDDHIST.
WOULD YOU MIND SPELLING IT
ALL OUT FOR ME?
>> I ALMOST PITY YOU,
SUCH IGNORANCE.
>> HA!
[ GROWLS ]
>> LET THERE BE LIGHT!
[ GROANS ]
>> YOUR MASTER, SHUTEN-DOJI,
HAS DIED BY MY HAND.
STARTING NOW, I AM YOUR LEADER.
UNDERSTOOD?
>> I SEE.
YOU HAVE A FONDNESS
FOR RENDING FLESH TO SHREDS.
THEN DO SO WITH
SHUTEN-DOJI’S CORPSE
SO THAT HE IS
FOREVER WITH YOU.
>> DAD.
AFTER YOU DIED, I PUT
YOUR SOTOBA ON MY FACE.
I SWORE THAT UNTIL WE BUILT
A DEMON WORLD THAT YOU AND ME
ALWAYS WANTED THAT I WOULD...
I WOULD BE YOUR GRAVESITE!
THAT’S WHAT I SWORE TO MYSELF
THE DAY YOU DIED, DAD!
>> VERY WELL, NOW.
I SHALL EXPLAIN IT TO YOU.
THIS NEEDLE PIERCES SINNERS.
THOSE WHO ATTEMPT TO MOVE
ARE DRIVEN MAD BY THE AGONY
AND CHOOSE DEATH.
>> MY STRENGTH’S FADING AND
MY EYES ARE GETTING BLURRY.
JUST WHAT ARE YOU?
>> BECAUSE YOU’RE SUCH
AN IGNORANT FOOL,
I SHALL TELL YOU.
LOOK UPON THIS BODY
GOD GRANTED ME!
BEHOLD THESE BEAUTIFUL WINGS
THAT ARE PROOF THAT I WAS BORN
AN ANGEL AND THESE
CELESTIAL COMPOUND EYES.
THIS SACRED VESSEL GLOWS
FROM WITHIN.
>> SHOKERA, AN INSECT YOKAI SAID
TO INFORM HEAVEN OF MAN’S SINS.
SO THIS IS HIS TRUE FORM.
>> IT IS CLEAR I AM
THE CHOSEN YOKAI!
>> WHAT’S GOING ON WITH HIM?
>> HIS SOTOBA FELL OFF.
TAKE COVER OR
WE’LL GET KILLED TOO!
>> LET’S DO IT TOGETHER.
DON’T YOU WORRY.
I CAN HEAR YOU LOUD
AND CLEAR, DAD.
YOU’RE HUNGRY FOR SOME BLOOD
AND YOU WANT TO RUN WILD.
>> WHAT IS THIS GUY?
>> HE’S ATTACKING!
>> I’LL CHOP YOU TO PIECES!
YOU’RE DONE.
DEVIL’S DRUM, THUNDER BARRAGE!
>> KUBINASHI, GET BACK!
[ GROWLS ]
>> DON’T BUTT IN!
>> DAMN IT!
>> I WANT TO SEE
EVEN MORE OF YOUR BLOOD.
>> KUBINASHI, NO!
[ GRUNTS ]
>> I AM THE INQUISITOR WHO
RENDERS JUDGMENT IN THE NAME
OF THE ALMIGHTY.
I PROTECT OUR DARK MOTHER
SO SHE MAY RESTORE NUE’S WORLD.
ALL WHO INTERFERE WILL BE
CHARGED FOR THAT CRIME
AND SENTENCED TO
THE HARSHEST PUNISHMENT.
>> LORD SHOKERA.
WE FOUND THESE HUMANS
IN THE ONMYOJI ESTATE.
>> BRING THEM HERE.
NO, SHE ISN’T AMONG THEM.
TELL ME, 27th HEIR,
WHERE CAN I FIND THAT GIRL
WHO SUMMONED HAGUN?
>> IF YOU MEAN YURA,
SHE’S OUT FIGHTING.
>> I DOUBT THAT VERY MUCH.
>> SEARCH THIS PLACE
ALL YOU WANT.
YOUR CHANCES OF FINDING HER
DWINDLE EVERY MINUTE.
IF YOU INTEND TO KILL ME, DO IT.
OUR FUTURE IS IN
THE NEXT GENERATION’S HANDS.
I KNOW YURA WILL
TAKE MY PLACE AND...
AH!
>> AS YOU WISH.
IT’S CLEAR THAT
YOU’RE NOT OF ANY USE.
>> 27th HEIR!
>> DAMN IT!
I CAN’T MOVE!
DAMN IT!
>> NOW THEN.
>> HEY!
THE KIDS HAVE NOTHING
TO DO WITH THIS,
SO JUST LET THEM GO.
>> COULD IT BE THAT THEY’RE
THE ONES YOU WISH TO PROTECT?
BUT THEY ARE INVOLVED.
EVERY HUMAN IS
TO BE SACRIFICED TO GOD.
[ GROWLS ]
>> MY LORD, WILL YOU ACCEPT
THE SINS OF THESE CHILDREN?
OH, MY LORD IN HEAVEN ABOVE,
I UNDERSTAND.
I SHALL SLAY THESE CHILDREN
AND DELIVER THEIR LIVERS
TO OUR DARK MOTHER.
[ LAUGHS ]
>> COME BACK, SOON, MR. MONK!
[ LAUGHTER ]
[ SCREAMING, LAUGHING ]
[ YELLS ]
>> I WAS SO CLOSE TO REGAINING
MY HUMANITY BACK THEN.
>> I’M SORRY, HOLY MAN.
I COULDN’T KEEP MY PROMISE,
BUT I DIDN’T HAVE
A CHOICE, DID I?
IT WAS ALL BECAUSE I HAD
TO PROTECT THEM
FROM THOSE BANDITS!
>> GET YOUR FILTHY HANDS AWAY
FROM THOSE KIDS RIGHT NOW!
>> LET THERE...
[ GRUNTS ]
>> LORD SHOKERA!
THIS CAN’T BE!
>> HEY, ONMYOJI, CAN YOU STAND?
>> WHO ARE YOU?
>> I’M AOTABO, A NOVICE
MONK FROM THE COUNTRYSIDE.
STAND YOUR GROUND.
THIS PLACE CAN’T FALL!
>> I CAME TO SEE
WHAT THE DELAY WAS.
WHY ARE YOU FOOLING
AROUND WITH THESE TWO?
>> SHUT UP!
I’M ABOUT TO FINISH
THIS, KIDOMARU.
>> KUBINASHI, I’M SO SORRY.
>> KINO!
>> YOU’LL BOTH BE IN HELL SOON.
[ GRUNTING ]
>> IS THIS A SEAL?
>> WHAT’S GOING ON HERE?
>> IT’S FUTILE.
ONCE THE SEAL IS IN PLACE,
NOT ONE OF YOUR KIND
CAN BREAK IT
EXCEPT YOUR MISTRESS,
BUT SHE’S CLAD IN HUMAN SKIN.
WELL DONE, YOKAI
OF THE NURA CLAN.
THE EIGHTH, SEVENTH AND SIXTH.
THAT’S THREE SEALS SO FAR.
SEE? ITS AS I TOLD YOU.
THEY’VE GONE ON THE DEFENSIVE
SINCE TAKING NIJO CASTLE.
>> HIDEMOTO! YOU AGAIN!
DAMN YOU, DOMAN ASHIYA’S HEIRS.
WE DEMONS WILL MAKE CERTAIN
TO GRIND YOU INTO DUST!
>> I SEE.
YOUR RESPONSE, YURA, DEAR?
>> JUST TRY IT IF YOU CAN.
DON’T UNDERESTIMATE HUMANS
OR YOU’LL BE SORRY!
>> ELOQUENTLY PUT, YURA, DEAR.
[ CRASHING ]
[ GRUNTING ]
[ YELLS ]
>> SO YOU’RE HIS GRANDSON!
I NEVER WOULD HAVE GUESSED,
GIVEN YOUR CURRENT APPEARANCE.
>> THIS YOKAI
KNOWS GRANDPA, TOO?
>> STILL, TO THINK YOU CAME
TO KYOTO SO UNPREPARED,
IT SEEMS YOU’RE JUST
AS FOOLISH AS YOUR
GRANDFATHER WAS!
YOUR STRENGTH IS
NO MATCH FOR MINE!
[ SHOUTS ]
>> HOW PATHETIC!
IS THAT ALL?
DIE!
>> A CERTAIN HEROIC BANDIT.
[ CHATTERING ]
>> IT’S TERRIBLY NOISY
OUTSIDE TONIGHT, ISN’T IT?
WHAT DID YOU DO THIS TIME?
>> WE STOLE FROM THE RICE
MERCHANT OVER IN OIKURA TOWN
AND WE GAVE AWAY
ALL THE MONEY WE FOUND
TO THE PEOPLE WHO LIVED THERE.
>> I SEE.
I HEARD THAT THE OWNER HAD
RENTED OUT THE ALLEY RESTAURANT
LAST MONTH AND THE MONTH
BEFORE THAT AS WELL.
IT SEEMS HE’S DOING
WELL FOR HIMSELF.
>> IT’S ALL DIRTY MONEY.
HE HAS TO EXPLOIT PEOPLE
TO RUN HIS BUSINESS.
SOMEONE HAS
TO JUDGE THE SINNERS.
>> MOST WOULD CONSIDER
YOU A SINNER, TOO.
THEY’LL BEHEAD YOU SOMEDAY.
JUST THE VERY THOUGHT OF IT
MAKES ME SHUDDER.
>> DON’T GET WORKED UP.
IF I AM CAUGHT, I’VE STILL
DISPENSED JUSTICE.
BEING JUDGED DOESN’T SCARE ME.
OH, IT’S BEEN A WHILE SINCE
I’VE SEEN YOU, LITTLE ONE.
>> I’M NOT LITTLE ANYMORE!
I’M ALREADY NINE YEARS OLD!
[ LAUGHS ]
>> ’TIL NEXT TIME.
>> KINO, COME IN NOW.
DON’T JUST STAND THERE.
>> COMING.
>> THE END.
>> I’M GOING TO DESTROY
ALL KYOTO YOKAI!
>> WE MUST FIGHT TOGETHER
AS WE DID IN THE PAST.
>> RIKUO, I WANT TO FIGHT
FOR YOU, TOO.
>> I WANT STRENGTH
FOR EVERYONE’S SAKE!