>> RIKUO?
>> DON’T WORRY.
I’M SURE HE’LL BE OKAY.
>> YES, YOU’RE RIGHT.
>> NURA CLAN,
EVEN WITH RIHAN NURA DEAD,
YOU STILL CONTINUE
TO GET IN MY WAY.
VERY WELL.
FOR CENTURIES, I HAD TO RELY
ON MY MOTHER AND HER MINIONS
TO DO MY BIDDING, BUT NO MORE.
AS YOU DO NOT SUPPORT ME,
YOU FACE DESTRUCTION
BY MY OWN HAND.
>> NURA!
>> YOU CAN’T START
WITHOUT A SIGNATURE WEAPON.
>> LET’S DO THIS, NURA...
ABE NO SEIMEI.
[ SHOUTS ]
>> FOLLOW HIS LEAD!
>> SO YOU’RE GOING TO KEEP
TRYING WITH A SWORD LIKE THAT?
[ SHOUTS ]
[ GRUNTS ]
[ SHOUTING ]
>> MASTER RIKUO!
>> A COURAGEOUS BUT
DOOMED OPPOSITION.
IT’S OVER.
DESTROY!
[ SHOUTING ]
>> MONSTER!
>> THIS IS CRAZY!
>> HE MEANS BUSINESS!
>> MASTER RIKUO!
EVERYONE...
[ LAUGHING ]
>> YOU’RE FINISHED!
FAREWELL, NURA CLAN!
THIS IS THE END!
[ LAUGHING ]
>> NOT QUITE YET.
>> HMM?
NO!
[ SCREAMS ]
>> LET’S GO.
WHO’S WITH ME?
>> WHAT?
>> ALL OF US HERE.
WE ARE.
>> MASTER RIKUO!
>> HOLD ON! WAIT FOR US!
>> WE’RE COMING TOO!
>> THE NIGHT PARADE OF
A HUNDRED DEMONS!
[ SHOUTS ]
[ GRUNTS ]
[ EXPLOSION ]
>> HUH?
[ CRASHES ]
>> RIKUO!
>> MASTER RIKUO!
>> UNBELIEVABLE!
>> NO WAY!
>> IS THERE NOTHING ELSE
WE CAN DO?
>> WHAT IS THIS?
>> SEIMEI’S ARM JUST--
>> HE DID IT!
>> HE DID?
YOU’VE GOT HIM, RIKUO!
[ CHEERING ]
>> ALL RIGHT!
[ LAUGHING ]
>> IT WOULD APPEAR THAT MY BODY
HASN’T ADAPTED
TO THIS WORLD JUST YET.
I HAVE NO CHOICE.
[ GASPING ]
[ DEMONS SHRIEKING ]
>> WHAT--WHAT IS THAT?
>> IT’S THE GATE TO HELL!
>> I’LL RETREAT FOR NOW.
YOU’VE DONE AN EXCELLENT JOB
THESE PAST THOUSAND YEARS,
KIDOMARU.
IBARAKI-DOJI, EVERY ONE
OF MY SERVANTS,
I’M RETURNING TO HELL.
COME.
>> YOU’RE GOING BACK?
>> HELL.
>> HELL?
>> YES, MY LORD SEIMEI.
>> WHAT’S WRONG?
AREN’T YOU GONNA GO?
BECAUSE I SURE AM.
>> IBARAKI?
I WASN’T WAVERING.
I WAS JUST MOVED BY THE OFFER!
>> ME, TOO!
>> LORD SEIMEI!
>> LORD NUE!
>> WAIT!
WHAT, GRAMPS?
>> WE SHALL MEET AGAIN SOON,
MY YOUNG LORD OF PANDEMONIUM.
>> HE’S GONE.
>> IS IT ALL OVER NOW?
>> IN ANY CASE, RIKUO DID IT!
HE CHASED THAT MONSTER AWAY!
[ SIGHING, CHUCKLING ]
>> MY LADY?
MY LADY!
MY LADY, PLEASE WAKE UP!
MY LADY?
BRING HER BACK!
[ CRIES ]
>> KYOKOTSU?
>> MY LADY, MY LADY!
>> RIKUO, RIKUO.
CLOSER.
I WANT TO GET A GOOD LOOK
AT YOUR FACE.
YOU LOOK EXACTLY LIKE HIM,
YOUR FATHER.
IF I COULD HAVE HAD A CHILD,
I’M SURE THAT HE WOULD
HAVE BEEN JUST LIKE YOU.
>> HUH?
HEY! HEY!
>> MY SON...WITH HIM.
>> OUR KID’S GOING TO GROW UP
TO BECOME THE NEXT LORD
OF PANDEMONIUM SOMEDAY
AND I WANT YOU BY MY SIDE
WHILE I STRENGTHEN OUR CLAN
FOR THE NEXT HEIR.
>> WHAT?
>> OTOME, BE WITH ME FOREVER.
>> MY LADY?
DON’T DIE!
MY LADY!
[ CRYING ]
>> GRAMPS?
I NEED STRENGTH.
I DON’T CARE HOW.
I HAVE TO BECOME STRONG.
>> RIKUO.
>> MAKE ME THE THIRD HEIR
RIGHT NOW.
[ COUGHS ]
>> HEY, LOOK, THE SKY!
>> THE SKY, IT’S CLEARING!
[ GASPING ]
>> HE WON.
RIKUO AND THE OTHERS DID IT.
>> YES.
>> YOU’RE SURE, RIKUO?
>> I’M SURE, DESPITE EVERYTHING.
IN THE END, SHE’S THEIR LEADER.
>> REALLY?
BUT I THOUGHT THE TWO OF YOU
WERE RELATED BY BLOOD
OR SOMETHING CLOSE TO IT.
EVEN IF YOU ARE, THOUGH,
SHE’S OUR SYMBOL.
THERE’S NO ONE ELSE IN
THE WORLD THAT WE WOULD FOLLOW.
SHE’S THE ONLY ONE.
>> RIKUO NURA, YOU HAVE
OUR THANKS.
>> SURE THING.
[ SINGING ]
>> THEY HAVE THEIR
OWN PRINCIPLES, BUT SEIMEI
BETRAYED THOSE BELIEFS,
SAID HE WAS THE LEADER
OF THE NIGHT PARADE
AND, WORSE, HE KILLED DAD
ALONG WITH THE WOMAN DAD LOVED.
HE WON’T GET AWAY
WITH ANY OF THAT.
>> RIKUO, DO YOU PLAN ON
HITTING HIM WITH ALL YOU’VE GOT?
>> YEAH. I’M GOING AFTER HIM.
>> YOU’RE TURNING INTO
A FINE MAN, RIKUO.
>> DON’T STOP ME.
GOT IT, GRAMPS?
>> RIKUO.
>> MASTER RIKUO?
>> WELL, WELL, WOULD YOU
LOOK AT THAT?
HE’S STARTING TO TALK
LIKE A REAL COMMANDER NOW.
>> YEAH, KIND OF, I SUPPOSE.
>> MASTER RIKUO...
>> WE’LL FOLLOW YOU
WHEREVER YOU GO.
[ CHEERING ]
>> THE TIME HAS FINALLY COME.
>> I KNEW I SHOULDN’T
HAVE COME TO KYOTO.
HOW COULD I NOT ACCEPT
THE BRAT AFTER SEEING THAT?
>> I GUESS THIS WILL
HAVE TO DO FOR NOW.
>> LET’S GO, GUYS.
STOP MOPING AROUND ALREADY!
>> BUT, KYOKOTSU...
>> SNAP OUT OF IT!
DO YOU WANT TO DISAPPOINT
OUR LADY WHEN SHE RETURNS?
>> OH?
>> AND SHE WILL RETURN ONE DAY.
UNTIL THAT TIME’S FINALLY HERE,
IT’S OUR DUTY TO MAKE SURE
HER HOST BODY
IS PROTECTED AT ALL COST!
>> I’LL GET REVENGE
FOR GRANDPA AND OUR FAMILY.
I SWEAR.
>> YURA?
SORRY, BUT I’VE GOT
A FAVOR TO ASK YOU.
>> HUH?
>> WHOA!
THE KEIKAIN MAIN HOUSE!
IT’S BEEN 400 YEARS!
>> AND IT LOOKS FINE.
IT’S ONLY SLIGHTLY DAMAGED.
>> I’M GLAD THAT SEIMEI DIDN’T
KILL EVERYONE OVER HERE.
>> HUH?
>> IT’S YOKAI!
>> WHAT THE HELL?
[ CHEERING, SHOUTING ]
>> HEY!
EVERYONE IN MY GROUP,
LINE UP NOW!
>> THIS BRINGS BACK MEMORIES
OF THAT DRUNKEN BASH
400 YEARS AGO!
>> WHAT IN THE WORLD ARE THESE
YOKAI EVEN DOING HERE?
>> EVEN 400 YEARS LATER,
YOUR CLAN IS STILL
AS LIVELY AS EVER.
>> WE TRY OUR BEST.
>> BUT YOU, ON THE OTHER HAND,
HAVE AGED QUITE A BIT.
AREN’T YOU YOKAI?
>> I’M NOT THE FREAK
OF NATURE HERE.
YOU DAMNED HUMAN!
>> I WONDER WHEN ABE NO SEIMEI
WILL RETURN FROM HELL.
>> HMM?
>> I’LL HAVE THEM LOOK INTO IT.
HIS BODY WAS NEARLY
COMPLETELY FORMED.
IT WON’T TAKE LONG.
I’LL RESEARCH THE SOUL REBIRTH
JUTSU AS IT’S SAID TO GIVE FLESH
PERPETUAL YOUTH AND LONGEVITY.
IT’S HARD TO SAY HOW LONG
AN AYAKASHI WOULD TAKE.
PERHAPS A YEAR.
>> A WHOLE YEAR.
>> BY THE WAY, I’D LIKE YOU
TO RETURN THE SWORD.
>> THAT’S WEIRD.
I JUST HAD IT.
>> THIS IS A NIGHTMARE.
NURARIHYON WAS THE ONE YOKAI
WHO WASN’T ALLOWED
IN THE HOUSE, AND WE STILL
HAVE TO DEAL WITH
ALL THE KYOTO YOKAI
WHO FLOODED IN WHEN
THE SEALS FELL.
I SWEAR.
>> SORRY.
>> IT WAS REALLY STUPID OF YOU.
LETTING KYOKOTSU AND THE OTHERS
GO WAS A BIG MISTAKE!
HONESTLY, UKIYOE TOWN’S
GOING TO HAVE TO WAIT.
>> I GUESS SO.
>> AKIFUSA!
>> YURA?
>> I’M THE NURA CLAN’S
YOUNG MASTER, RIKUO NURA.
YURA WAS TELLING ME,
IN THE KEIKAIN CLAN,
YOU’RE THE BEST
AT MAKING SPIRIT BLADES.
>> WHAT?
>> HERE.
MY REQUEST IS FOR A SWORD
THAT SURPASSES THIS ONE.
>> WHAT?
>> ONE THAT CAN BEAT SEIMEI.
>> NURA?
>> PLEASE SAY YES.
LET’S FIGHT TOGETHER.
>> I’M HAPPY TO ASSIST AS WELL.
>> HIDEMOTO!
>> I’LL POUND EVERYTHING
THAT I KNOW INTO YOU.
PLUS I KNOW YOU CAN DO IT!
>> IF YOU ALLOW ME TO,
I’D CONSIDER IT AN HONOR.
>> THANK YOU.
>> HE’S AGREEING
TO HELP A YOKAI.
>> YOKAI ARE EVIL.
SHOULD WE DESTROY HIM, RYUJI?
>> NAH, THAT’S FINE.
YOU’RE STILL BADLY INJURED,
SO TAKE IT EASY.
>> HEY, THERE!
YOU’RE HERE, NURA!
>> RIKUO!
SO YOU DID COME HERE.
>> KANA, KYOTSUGU,
GOOD TO SEE YOU!
>> YOU’RE WAY BEYOND SUPER LATE,
NURA!
WHAT IS WRONG WITH YOU?
>> SORRY ABOUT THAT.
>> WE CAN FINALLY GO HOME.
>> JUST LOOK!
YOKAI ARE RESPONSIBLE
FOR ALL THIS!
>> YOU DON’T SAY?
>> SO HOW’D YOU GET HERE?
>> MISS OIKAWA!
IT LOOKS LIKE YOU’RE
SAFE AND SOUND!
>> OH! YOU GUYS OUGHT
TO STAY OVER HERE.
>> COME TO THINK OF IT,
IT’S PRETTY NOISY OVER THERE.
>> IT’S NOTHING, HONEST.
>> WHAT ARE YOU TRYING
TO HIDE, NURA?
>> RIKUO?
>> IS THERE SOMETHING
YOU DON’T WANT US TO SEE?
>> YEAH. WHAT’S GOING ON?
>> THE AREA’S OFF LIMITS,
YOU SEE!
>> YOU CAN’T GO THERE.
>> SOMETHING’S FISHY.
>> YOU SAID IT!
>> SEIMEI, SANMOTO GOROZAEMON,
MY FATHER’S KILLERS,
AND THE ARCHENEMIES
OF THE NURA CLAN.
>> OH, IS THIS SPOT TAKEN?
>> HUH?
>> WHAT ARE YOU GUYS?
YOU BOTH HAVE HAIR LIKE MINE.
[ LAUGHS ]
I’D SAY THAT’S YOUR FAULT,
BUT WHATEVER.
THE WORLD SURE IS A FUNNY PLACE.
>> DAD?
THEN THIS IS...
> HEY, THERE.
I’M NURARIHYON,
THE LORD OF PANDEMONIUM,
AND I WANT THE TWO OF YOU
TO JOIN MY HUNDRED DEMONS.
[ LAUGHS ]
>> WHAT ARE YOU GOING ON ABOUT?
I’M THE RULER OF EDO,
THE SECOND HEIR, RIHAN NURA.
REMEMBER THAT,
AND I’LL DEFEND THAT TITLE.
>> OH, YEAH?
LET’S DO IT THEN.
I’LL BE GLAD TO TAKE
THAT TITLE AWAY FROM YOU.
>> HOLD ON THERE.
I DON’T FIGHT ALONE AND
KUBINASHI SHOULD BE ON HIS WAY.
>> JUST HOLD ON A MINUTE,
YOU TWO!
>> HUH?
>> WHAT I MEAN IS, DAMN IT ALL!
QUIT DECIDING
THESE THINGS ON YOUR OWN!
AFTER ALL, I’M THE YOUNG MASTER.
>> I SWEAR.
>> LOOKS LIKE WE’VE GOT
NO CHOICE, HUH?
[ GRUNTING ]
>> WHAT THE HELL?
>> LET ME JOIN IN.
[ SHOUTS ]
>> WHAT’S WITH THIS
LITTLE RUNT OVER HERE?
HE’S PUTTING A DAMPER
ON ALL OUR FUN.
>> DON’T BE STINGY.
YOU’LL NEVER BE
POPULAR WITH THE LADIES.
[ CHUCKLING ]
>> HEY!
DAMN IT!
QUIT IGNORING ME LIKE THAT!
AND STAY STILL!
>> COME ON!
I’M RIGHT OVER HERE!
YOU’RE BAD AT THIS.
YOU EVEN TRYING?
[ SHOUTS ]
>> I CAN’T BELIEVE
YOU’RE TEAMING UP!
YOU’RE SLIPPERY LIKE EELS.
[ CHUCKLING ]
>> DAMN IT!
>> HEY, WHAT’S WRONG, KID?
YOU GIVING UP?
>> SHUT UP!
I’M JUST RESTING.
>> I’M KIND OF BORED
WITH SPARRING ANYWAY.
SHALL WE?
>> SURE.
>> HOLD ON. WHAT NOW?
>> OH, THIS ISN’T FOR
LITTLE BRATS LIKE YOU.
>> YEAH. IT’S SOMETHING THAT
ONLY US GROWNUPS CAN ENJOY.
>> LITTLE BRAT?
WHATEVER.
BUT STILL, THIS IS NICE.
AND BEING HERE
LIKE THIS WITH GRAMPS
AND DAD, THE THREE OF US.
>> HEY, RIKUO?
DON’T FALL ASLEEP THERE.
YOU’LL JUST CATCH A COLD
IF YOU DO.
>> DAD?
>> YOU’RE GONNA BE STANDING
AT THE HELM OF THE NURA CLAN
STARTING NOW.
THIRD HEIR,
WE’RE COUNTING ON YOU.
>> RIGHT.
>> OH, RIKUO, ARE YOU UP NOW?
>> I GUESS SO.
>> I SUPPOSE THE DREAM
YOU WERE HAVING WAS NICE.
>> WHAT?
>> YOU WERE SMILING
IN YOUR SLEEP.
[ LAUGHING ]
>> OH, MASTER!
YOU’D BETTER COME WITH ME.
YOU HAVE TO GET READY
AND QUICKLY, TOO.
>> HEY!
WHAT ARE YOU SO EXCITED FOR?
>> THERE’S ONLY ONE REASON
I COULD BE.
BECAUSE, AFTER ALL...
[ GIGGLES ]
>> YEAH, I KNOW.
IT’S TODAY.
>> IS HE HERE YET?
IT’S ALMOST TIME.
[ MURMURING ]
>> THANK YOU FOR WAITING.
WE’RE ABOUT TO WAGE
AN ALL-OUT WAR
AGAINST NUE AND HIS MINIONS
WHO WILL RISE FROM HELL.
THIS WILL BE A BATTLE OF FEAR
AND NOTHING TO SNEEZE AT.
MY GRANDSON WILL BE
IN COMMAND NOW.
THIS WAS A UNANIMOUS VOTE
BY THE TOP LEADERS
OF THE NURA CLAN, UNDERSTOOD?
[ MURMURING ]
>> I’D LIKE TO BEGIN
WITH A FEW WORDS.
FIRST OF ALL, I WON’T
TOLERATE HARMING HUMANS.
FURTHER, I WON’T TOLERATE
BREAKING OUR CODE EVEN IF YOU
MIGHT LOSE TO OTHER YOKAI.
IN OTHER WORDS, HOLD ONTO
YOUR FEAR AS AYAKASHI,
NO MATTER WHAT.
THAT’S THE KIND OF CLAN
THAT I INTEND TO ESTABLISH,
THE THIRD HEIR’S NIGHT PARADE
OF A HUNDRED DEMONS.
GOT IT?