[ GRUNTS ]
>> BEHOLD MY SECRET TECHNIQUE
FOR MY MASTER,
FOR MY LORD SEIMEI’S
LONGSTANDING WISH.
[ CHATTERING ]
>> SEIMEI?
>> HE RULED KYOTO’S
DARKNESS A THOUSAND YEARS AGO.
HE WAS AN ONMYOJI.
>> WHAT’S HE TALKING ABOUT?
SEIMEI?
I THOUGHT
THAT THEIR LONGSTANDING WISH
WAS NUE’S RESURRECTION?
>> IT SEEMS MY SUSPICIONS
WERE CORRECT.
HE’S THE LEGENDARY
ONMYOJI OF THE HEIAN ERA.
ALSO, HIS MOTHER WAS A FOX
OR SO THE STORIES WOULD SUGGEST.
THE HUMAN WORLD
WAS HIS PLAYTHING,
BUT HE CONTROLLED
A HUNDRED DEMONS
OF HIS OWN, TOO.
HIS NAME WAS ABE NO SEIMEI.
>> I REACHED MY PEAK
AFTER A THOUSAND YEARS.
I CAN’T POSSIBLY GO ANY FASTER.
THAT’S WHY I CHANGED
MY BLADES INSTEAD.
YOUR BODY WILL EXPERIENCE
THIS DIVINE SPEED
FIRSTHAND AND HEAD ON!
SLASH, INFINITE.
THERE’S NO ESCAPE.
THIS TECHNIQUE PRODUCES
TENS OF THOUSANDS
OF BLADES.
TURN INTO DUST!
[ GRUNTING ]
>> THIS ISN’T
JUST KURO’S FEAR.
IT’S THE FUSING
OF BOTH OUR FEAR.
EQUIP, MELD!
HAVE YOU FORGOTTEN?
YOU’VE SEEN MINE BEFORE.
>> KIDOMARU!
>> GET IT NOW?
THAT’S OUR LEADER.
HE REALLY HAS GROWN.
THERE’S ABSOLUTELY NO WAY
OUR HUNDRED DEMONS
WILL LOSE, OR ME.
NOT TO YOU.
>> WHAT KIND OF GARBAGE
ARE YOU GOING ON ABOUT?
>> IT’S BEEN SO LONG.
SO MUCH TIME HAS PASSED.
THIS ONE MOMENT, COMPARED
TO THOSE THOUSAND YEARS WAITED,
HOLDS NO MEANING AT ALL.
BUT IT IS A MOMENT
I HAVE NO REGRET SECURING.
[ GASPS ]
>> WHAT’S THAT?
>> DAMN IT!
WE’RE TOO LATE.
[ MUTTERING ]
[ SHOUTING ]
>> WATCH OUT!
>> WHAT YOU SEE IS OUR
LONGSTANDING WISH, RIKUO NURA.
>> I CAN FEEL YOU, SEIMEI.
>> IS THAT HAGOROMO-GITSUME?
>> I HAVE WAITED
A THOUSAND YEARS
FOR THIS POINT,
THIS MOMENT, THE BIRTH OF NUE,
THE NEW LORD OF PANDEMONIUM
AND RULER OF AYAKASHI
AND MEN IS NEARLY AT HAND.
IT IS GOOD THAT YOU ARE
ALL GATHERED HERE
ON THIS AUSPICIOUS DAY.
>> SAY WHAT?
>> SOME HAIL FROM KYOTO
WHILE OTHERS HAVE JOURNEYED
FAR FROM EDO AND TONO
TO GIVE US THEIR BLESSING.
TO EACH AND EVERY AYAKASHI,
I COMMEND YOU ALL.
[ CHEERING ]
>> SUCH ENTHUSIASM.
YOU WISH TO CELEBRATE?
WELL, BY ALL MEANS THEN,
MY DARLING MINIONS.
>> HEY, WHAT’S
THE DEAL WITH HER?
SHE’S TREATING US
LIKE WE’RE GUESTS.
>> HAGOROMO-GITSUNE?
IS THAT HER?
>> I THINK SO.
>> HEY, KUBINASHI,
THAT FACE OF HERS.
>> NO WAY.
IT ISN’T POSSIBLE.
>> MOTHER?
MOTHER.
>> WHAT THE HELL?
>> WHAT IS THAT UP THERE?
[ LAUGHS ]
>> IT’S ABOUT TO BE BORN.
LADY HAGOROMO-GITSUME’S
ACHIEVED OUR
LONGSTANDING WISH!
THINGS HAVE GONE SMOOTHLY
JUST AS WE PLANNED.
>> LONG AGO, THERE WAS
DARKNESS ALONG WITH HUMANS.
WE, THE CREATURES OF THE DARK,
EXISTED SIDE
BY SIDE WITH MANKIND.
BUT HUMANS WERE UNABLE
TO MAINTAIN A GRACEFUL LIFE.
BEFORE LONG, THEIR TRUE
SORDID NATURES
TOOK HOLD OF THEIR HEARTS.
THOSE WE ONCE TRUSTED
AND LOVED BETRAYED US
FOR CENTURIES AND WE DESPAIRED
WITH EVERY ACT OF TREACHERY.
I LONGED TO DEDICATE MYSELF
TO FILLING THIS WORLD WITH
SOMETHING PURE ONE DAY,
SOMETHING DARK AS FAR
AS THE EYE COULD SEE,
THE PUREST BLACK LACKING
EVEN THE MOST MINUTE FLAW.
MUCH LIKE MY BLACK HAIR,
MY BLACK CLOTHING
AND MY PITCH BLACK EYES
AS WELL,
AN ABSOLUTE DARKNESS.
NOW THEN, MY SERVANTS
OF PURE DARKNESS,
PROTECT HIM.
[ GROWLING ]
>> THEY’RE COMING!
>> IS IT ME OR ARE THERE
MORE NOW?
>> WE FAILED.
WE COULDN’T STOP NUE’S BIRTH.
>> WAIT.
DID SHE SAY PROTECT HIM?
SO DOES THAT MEAN
NUE CAN’T FIGHT?
>> YOU’RE RIGHT.
IF THEY’RE GUARDING HIM,
THEN PERHAPS HE CAN’T.
IT’S CLEAR HE HASN’T
YET FULLY FORMED.
NUE WAS HUMAN ONCE
AND HE CAN STILL
BE STOPPED WITH
NENEKIRIMARU AND OUR HAGUN.
[ GROWLS ]
>> PROTECT MASTER RIKUO!
[ SINGING ]
>> THIS IS OUR LADY’S
LONGSTANDING WISH!
I WON’T LET YOU DESTROY IT!
>> YURA, I’M HEADING
FOR THE TOP.
JUST TRY TO KEEP UP.
>> YOU GOT IT!
I HAVE TO PROTECT KYOTO.
IT’S MY DUTY AS AN ONMYOJI!
>> HMM?
AND WHO MIGHT YOU BE?
>> HAGOROMO-GITSUME
TO PROTECT KYOTO.
YOU MUST DIE!
DEMONIC POSSESSION LANCE!
>> AKIFUSA!
>> KYOTO’S IN RUINS
AND NAYAKASHI ARE
RUNNING RAMPANT!
I REFUSE TO ALLOW THE KEIKAIN
CLAN TO END WITH YOUR VICTORY!
FOR THE SAKE OF JUSTICE
AS WELL THIS CITY,
I IMBUE MYSELF OF
THIS FORBIDDEN JUTSU!
>> OH, YOU AGAIN.
PLAYING WITH YOU HAS
LOST ITS APPEAL.
[ GROANS ]
[ GASP ]
>> YOU FOUGHT TO
THE BITTER END.
WHAT A PATHETIC FOOL.
YOUR PART IN ALL
THIS HAS LONG BEEN OVER,
YET STILL YOU STRUGGLE.
>> AKIFUSA, YOU CAN’T DIE!
>> RUN, KYOGEN.
>> WATER?
>> BIG BROTHER!
>> THAT GARBAGE AKIFUSA
SPOUTS WORKED REALLY WELL
AND THE LOOK ON HIS FACE
WOULD MAKE ANYBODY BELIEVE
THAT HE’D FIGHT TIL
HIS DYING BREATH.
YOU SEE, I FIGURED
YOU’D GET BORED PRETTY QUICK
AND TRY TO TAKE HIM DOWN
RIGHT AWAY.
NOW, MAMIRU.
LEARN THIS, MAMIRU.
WATER AND LIGHTNING MIX.
DESTROY.
MAMIRU?
>> WHAT NONSENSE WAS THAT?
WAS IT YOUR INTENTION
TO DECEIVE ME?
AN ONMYOJI AND A LIAR THEN.
I PRESUME YOU SHALL BE
THE NEXT TO ENTERTAIN ME.
>> WHAT ARE YOU
TALKING ABOUT?
FIGHTING YOU ISN’T
WHAT I’VE GOT ON MY MIND
IN THE LEAST.
>> WHAT?
>> MY LADY! BEHIND YOU!
>> BECOME THE SEAL’S
CORNERSTONE TO ONCE AGAIN
PURGE THE AYAKASHI FROM KYOTO!
>> YOU BASTARD!
>> DESTROY!
I ONLY WANTED YOUR ATTENTION
ON SOMETHING ELSE
AND ALL I NEEDED
WAS A FEW MOMENTS.
[ GRUNTING ]
>> THAT’S IMPOSSIBLE!
>> LOOK, THAT GUY
SEALED NUE JUST LIKE
HE DID SENJU-MUKADE!
>> MY BROTHER DID IT!
>> THAT WAS A CLOSE ONE.
>> IT’S TSUCHI-GUMO!
>> HEY, HAGOROMO-GITSUNE,
YOU SHOULDN’T TAKE YOUR EYES
OFF YOUR KID LIKE THAT.
YOU’RE HIS MOTHER, RIGHT?
[ GRUNTS ]
>> ONMYOJI?
[ GASPS ]
YOU!
>> WE FINALLY MEET,
HAGOROMO-GITSUNE.
>> HAGOROMO-GITSUNE!
THAT FACE!
I KNOW IT!
>> WHO ARE YOU, LADY?
WHO’S THAT OVER THERE?
>> SO IT WAS YOU THEN.
YOU’RE THE ONE WHO
KILLED MY OLD MAN!
>> THAT COUNTENANCE.
NURARIHYON, YOU WOULD DARE
GET IN MY WAY AGAIN?
[ GROANS ]
>> WHAT ARE YOU DOING?
DON’T JUST SIT THERE!
>> HUH?
>> WHAT THE...?
WHEN DID HE GET UP THERE.
>> QUIT FOOLING AROUND,
GASHADOKURO.
WE NEED TO GET UP
TO THE TOP RIGHT NOW!
>> ALL RIGHT.
[ SCREAMS ]
>> WHAT’S THE RUSH?
WE’RE JUST GETTING STARTED HERE.
>> WHAT? GO AWAY!
[ GROANING ]
>> TRY TO HANG
IN THERE, SHOEI.
MASTER RIKUO WILL WIN.
I KNOW IT.
>> WHAT A DESPICABLE FACE.
WHY DOES YOUR BLOODLINE
STYMIE THE CREATION
OF A WORLD WHERE AYAKASHI REIGN?
I COULD NEVER FATHOM IT.
>> IS THAT THE REASON
YOU KILLED MY OLD MAN?
>> AGAIN WITH THAT DRIVEL.
WHAT?
>> HEY, DON’T TELL ME
THAT YOU DON’T REMEMBER.
YOU DON’T.
>> COME ON.
YOU GUYS HAVE A LONG-RUNNING
GRUDGE TO SETTLE, RIGHT?
HURRY UP AND GO AT IT.
AND DON’T WORRY.
I’LL BE MORE THAN HAPPY
TO BABYSIT NUE.
JUST GO AHEAD
AND ENJOY YOUR FIGHT.
>> I NEEDN’T PRATTLE ON.
I INTENDED TO!
[ GRUNTS ]
[ SCREAMS ]
>> I’VE HAD THIS SINCE
MY TIME WITH THE HEIKE CLAN,
THE FAN OF TWO TAILS.
I SHALL ERADICATE
THE BLOODLINE OF
THAT INSUFFERABLE NURARIHYON.
[ SCREAMS ]
>> I ENDED UP BEING
THE ONE NEEDING SAVING.
I GUESS I SHOULD
THANK YOU FOR THAT.
HA!
THE PLAN WAS TO SEAL NUE
AND THEN JUST KEEP
AN EYE ON THINGS FROM
A NICE SAFE DISTANCE.
THE YOKAI WOULD TURN
ON EACH OTHER
AND WE COULD JUST THROW
A LITTLE PARTY OR SOMETHING.
>> THAT’S JUST LIKE YOU,
AS PRACTICAL AS EVER.
>> SO HOW DO YOU PLAN
TO BEAT HER?
SHE’S STRONGER NOW
THAN 400 YEARS AGO.
>> I’LL MAKE NENEKIRIMARU
REACH HER SOMEHOW.
I WON’T KNOW IF I CAN
BEAT HER OR NOT UNTIL I TRY.
I JUST HAVE TO FIGHT!
>> YOU SHOULD TEAM UP
WITH MAMIRU.
>> HUH?
WITH MAMIRU?
>> TEAM UP WITH HER?
IS THAT A
DIRECT ORDER, RYUJI?
>> THERE’S NO CHOICE.
NUE WILL HAVE TO WAIT.
YOU NEED TO GO AND BACK HIM UP
BECAUSE WE’RE GONNA BE
TAKING HER OUT HERE AND NOW.
>> A THOUSAND BLADES.
I CAN SEE WHY KIDOMARU LOST.
HOWEVER, YOUR VAUNTED
SWORD SHALL NEVER TOUCH ME.
>> MY SWORD.
>> MASTER? MASTER?
>> KURO?
>> THIS WON’T DO.
YOU MUST CREATE AN OPENING
FOR YOURSELF
AND CLOSE THE DISTANCE.
>> AN OPENING?
BUT HOW?
>> THE STRIKE METHOD.
RELEASE ME WHILE USING IT.
I WILL MAKE SURE THAT
I CONNECT WITH ALL
NINE OF HER TAILS,
SO PLEASE
USE THAT OPPORTUNITY
TO FIND YOUR DECISIVE BLOW.
>> BUT IF WE REALLY DO THIS,
THEN YOU’LL BE...
ALL RIGHT.
SO YOUR LIFE’S IN MY HANDS.
>> WHAT WAS THAT, HUH?
[ GRUNTING ]
>> ITAKU!
[ GRUNTS ]
>> DAMN YOU TWO!
[ CACKLING ]
>> SHOEI!
ARE YOU OKAY?
>> THIS IS WHERE YOU DIE.
[ GASPS ]
[ SHOUTS ]
>> DAMN SNAKES!
>> I DON’T CARE IF YOU’RE
FROM TONO OR WHEREVER!
OUT OF THE WAY!
[ SHOUTING, CLANGING ]
>> HEY, WOULD YOU
HURRY UP, PLEASE?
>> I’M SORRY THAT I CAN’T BE
AT YOUR SIDE NOW, RIKUO.
>> MIZUCHI BALLS!
>> BLAH!
>> THERE’S NO END TO THIS!
[ GROANS ]
>> HUH?
THE SANBA-GARASU!
SHOULDN’T YOU BE
GUARDING OUR HOME?
>> WE ACCOMPANIED
OUR FATHER HERE.
>> BY THE WAY,
HAVE YOU SEEN HIM?
>> HE SHOULD BE
SOMEWHERE NEARBY.
HE CAME HERE IN SEARCH OF
THE SUPREME COMMANDER.
>> ANOTHER ATTACK?
>> IT’S FATHER!
>> SUPREME COMMANDER!
>> I SWEAR.
AND YOU KEPT NAGGING ME
TO STAY HIDDEN, TOO.
>> OF COURSE, I NAGGED AT YOU!
THE SUPREME COMMANDER
SHOULDN’T BE SO CLOSE
TO THE BATTLE!
>> WELL, WHY’D YOU COME HERE?
>> I JUST WANTED
TO CHECK SOMETHING OUT.
BUT STILL,
WHO COULD HAVE GUESSED?
THAT FACE OF HERS,
IT’S ONE THAT I RECOGNIZE.
>> LET’S GO, KURO.
[ SHOUTS ]
>> YOUR GRANDFATHER
USED THE SAME SILLY TRICK
400 YEARS AGO.
AS YOU CAN SEE,
IT WON’T WORK A SECOND TIME.
THE SWORD OF THREE TAILS!
I’VE LONG DREAMT OF ERADICATING
YOUR BLOODLINE WITH THIS SWORD.
[ GROANS ]
>> YOUR LIVER BELONGS TO ME.
[ GASPS ]
[ GRUNTS ]
>> I MISSED?
HOW VERY ODD.
I WAS SO CERTAIN THAT
I HAD PIERCED YOUR HEART.
IT WOULD APPEAR THAT
YOU’RE AS SLIPPERY AS AN EEL.
AS I SAID, I INTEND
TO DEVOUR YOUR BLOOD AND LIVER.
[ PANTS ]
>> MASTER RIKUO!
>> NURA!
MAMIRU, LET’S GO!
>> WAIT!
>> NURA?
>> TELL ME, WHEN DID YOU
TURN INTO HAGOROMO-GITSUNE?
I REMEMBER SEEING YOU
WHEN I WAS A KID
AND HOW YOU LOOKED SO HAPPY.
[ GIGGLING ]
>> WHAT?
>> TELL ME.
I’M ASKING THE HUMAN
PART OF YOU.
[ GASPS ]
>> HUH?
[ LAUGHS ]
>> I’M GOING TO HAVE
TO ASK YOU TO GET
OUT OF MY WAY, TSUCHI-GUMO.
[ LAUGHS ]
YOU JUST WANT TO FIGHT NUE.
ISN’T THAT RIGHT?
I WON’T LET YOU.
>> HOLD ON.
WHO THE HELL ARE YOU?
YOU WEREN’T HERE
400 YEARS AGO.
[ LAUGHING ]
>> ANSWER ME, OLD MAN.
HOW LONG HAVE YOU BEEN
AT HAGOROMO-GITSUNE’S SIDE?
>> THAT CHILD BELONGS TO US.
[ LAUGHS ]
>> IT’S NOT ENOUGH.
THERE’S NOT ENOUGH BLOOD!
>> I WILL PROTECT YURA.
>> LET’S GO.
WE’RE DRAWING
THE CURTAIN ON THIS ACT.
>> THIS TIME, IT SHALL
TRULY BE THE END!