[ GASPING ]
>> WHAT’S GOING ON?
[ GASPS ]
[ SHOUTS ]
>> RIKUO, COULD THIS FEAR
BE YOURS?
>> LORD GYUKI!
>> WHAT HAPPENED HERE?
>> THE TENGU CAME
OUT OF NOWHERE!
[ SHOUTS ]
>> RIKUO, THAT FEAR!
>> GYUKI, IS THIS THE TECHNIQUE?
[ GROANING ]
>> HE USED MY POISON WINGS?
DAD, IS THIS WHAT YOU MEANT
BY SPREADING OUR WINGS
FOR THE NIGHT PARADE?
>> THIS CAN’T BE HAPPENING!
IT’S IMPOSSIBLE, INSANE!
THEY ARE MT. KURAMA’S ELITE!
GYUKI, I DEMAND ANSWERS AT ONCE!
WHAT DID YOU TEACH HIM?
>> THAT ISN’T A DETAIL
THAT YOU NEED TO KNOW, TENGU.
IT’S A SPECIAL TECHNIQUE
OF THE NURA CLAN.
YOU SEE IT NOW, DON’T YOU?
IT’S NOT JUST ABOUT PROTECTING
OTHERS OR BEING PROTECTED.
IT’S ABOUT MUTUAL TRUST
AND IT’S THE ABILITY
TO FORM THOSE BONDS
THAT ENABLED YOU TO MASTER
THE TECHNIQUE OF THE LORD
OF A HUNDRED DEMONS.
>> I SEE.
UP UNTIL NOW, I’VE BEEN TRYING
TO HANDLE EVERYTHING
ALL ON MY OWN.
GYUKI, THANKS FOR THE HELP.
I GET IT NOW.
>> THIS IS THE FINAL STEP.
USE THE TECHNIQUE YOU JUST
LEARNED TO CUT THROUGH MY FEAR.
>> RIGHT.
>> IT’S BEEN A FEW DAYS.
WHERE IS THAT BRAT?
>> MASTER RIKUO...
>> TSURARA, GUESS WHAT HAPPENED?
ZEN CAME BY TO PLAY
WITH ME TODAY!
>> OH, REALLY?
IT SOUNDS LIKE YOU HAD FUN.
>> YEAH, AND HE THINKS
I’D MAKE A
GREAT SUPREME COMMANDER!
[ LAUGHS ]
>> I DO, TOO, AND I’LL BE SURE
TO PROTECT YOU ’TIL
YOU’RE READY TO TAKE OVER.
>> NO, YOU’RE NOT!
I’M GONNA PROTECT YOU, TSURARA!
>> BECOME A GREAT COMMANDER,
ONE WHO PROTECTS
ALL THOSE WHO ARE
IMPORTANT TO HIM.
LOOK, AO.
THE MASTER FINISHED GRADE SCHOOL
WITHOUT NOTICING
THAT WE WERE WITH HIM ALL ALONG.
>> YEAH.
LOOKS LIKE OUR JOB
HERE IS DONE NOW.
>> WELL, MAYBE FOR YOU,
BUT I PLAN
TO PROTECT MASTER FOR
THE REST OF MY LIFE.
[ CRYING ]
MASTER RIKUO?
[ THUNDER ]
>> HOW ARE REIRA
AND DOHIKO DOING?
>> YUKARI’S WITH THEM.
I’M SURE THEY’LL BE FINE.
>> YEAH, THAT’S TRUE.
>> RIKUO, YOU’VE GOT
A STAKE IN THIS.
THAT’S WHY WE AGREED TO WAIT
LIKE THAT GYUKI GUY SAID TO,
BUT WE’VE WAITED LONG ENOUGH.
IF YOU DON’T SHOW UP
BY MIDNIGHT TONIGHT,
THEN WE’LL KILL TSUCHI-GUMO.
>> POOR YURA.
SHE MUST BE EXHAUSTED.
>> I DON’T BELIEVE IT!
THE YOKAI MADE IT ALL THE WAY
TO OUR DOORSTEP
AND I SOMEHOW ENDED UP
FALLING ASLEEP AGAIN!
HOW OBLIVIOUS CAN A PERSON BE?
>> HEY, KIYOTSUGU!
>> IS THAT ALL YOU CAN SAY?
>> SO HOW BAD IS IT?
>> WE NOT ONLY LOST
THE 27th HEIR,
BUT MANY OF OUR
SKILLED CASTERS AS WELL.
>> AND WITH YURA STILL OUT COLD,
I GUESS THERE’S NOT MUCH
WE CAN DO RIGHT NOW.
WELL, THAT’S JUST GREAT.
>> YOU DON’T INTEND
TO GIVE UP, RYUJI, DO YOU?
>> HMM.
>> OH, HOLD ON!
>> YOU’RE SUPPOSED
TO PROTECT THIS PLACE.
>> YUKI-ONNA TOLD ME TO
AND SHE’S BEEN CAPTURED.
ARE YOU SAYING I SHOULD
JUST SIT HERE?
JUST DEFENDING THIS PLACE
WON’T PROTECT ANYONE.
>> BUT, AO--
>> EVEN SO, TRY TO PUT UP
WITH IT FOR NOW.
IF ANGER CLOUDS YOUR JUDGMENT
AND WHAT’S IMPORTANT,
WE’LL BE LOST.
SO PLEASE.
>> WE GOT BEAT BAD.
HOW ARE THINGS GONNA
GO FROM HERE?
>> IT’S NOT LIKE 400 YEARS AGO.
>> KEJORO SAID TO KEEP
THE NIGHT PARADE GOING.
BUT THE WAY THINGS ARE...
>> HEY, REIRA.
>> YOU SHOULDN’T BE
STANDING OUT HERE.
IT ISN’T GOOD FOR YOU.
>> WHAT’S THE MATTER?
>> REIRA?
WHAT’S WRONG?
>> HUH?
>> WHAT’S GOING ON DOWN THERE?
WHOA!
[ CHATTERING ]
>> REIRA?
DOHIKO?
>> JUST GO.
DON’T WORRY ABOUT US.
WE’LL BOTH BE
ALL RIGHT OVER HERE.
NOTHING BAD WILL HAPPEN AS
LONG AS YUKARI’S WITH US.
>> LOOKS LIKE YOU’RE ALL
BETTER NOW.
>> THANKS FOR EVERYTHING.
I SWEAR I’LL REPAY
MY DEBT TO TONO.
>> IT’S MASTER RIKUO!
HEY, WAIT FOR ME!
>> COME ON!
>> WE’LL BE RIGHT BEHIND YOU,
KO-ONI!
>> THE NURA CLAN’S
GONNA KICK SOME BUTT!
>> YEAH!
[ GIGGLES ]
>> I WONDER WHICH ONE OF YOU
I SHOULD CHOOSE.
I KNOW OUR LADY PREFERS
TO HAVE SLENDER GIRLS
TO DINE ON RIGHT
AFTER WAKING UP.
SHE SAYS THEIR FLAVOR
IS A REFRESHING ONE.
IT’S SO HARD TO DECIDE.
[ LAUGHS ]
>> PARDON ME, MY LORD.
>> REPORT!
>> SOMEONE ATTACKED
THE AYAKASHI AT SEIEIJI TEMPLE
AND EXTERMINATED
EVERY LAST ONE OF THEM.
>> THAT’S NOTHING TO BE
CONCERNED ABOUT...WHAT?
HOW COULD SOMETHING
LIKE THIS HAVE HAPPENED?
WHO COULD HAVE BEATEN THEM?
NEITHER THE NURA CLAN NOR
THE ONMYOJI HAVE THE STRENGTH
FOR A COUNTEROFFENSIVE
RIGHT NOW!
GIVE ME THAT!
>> RIGHT.
>> HMM?
THE SMOKE’S COMING
FROM SEIEIJI TEMPLE!
SO IT WAS TRUE!
BUT WHO COULD HAVE DONE THIS?
>> REPORTING.
>> DON’T BOTHER ME RIGHT NOW!
THIS ISN’T THE TIME...
>> THE FOURTH SEAL AT
NISHIHOGANJI TEMPLE
WAS ATTACKED FROM THE EAST
AN HOUR AGO AND THE AYAKASHI
THERE WERE ALL DECIMATED.
>> WHAT?
>> AND REPORTS INDICATE THAT
THE ATTACKERS ARE NOW HEADING
TOWARDS THE WEST AND THE NORTH.
>> WHAT WAS THAT YOU JUST SAID?
[ GROANS ]
>> REPORTING IN, SIR.
THE THIRD SEAL WAS
JUST ATTACKED.
THE AYAKASHI STATIONED AT
ROKUKINJI TEMPLE WERE
SLAUGHTERED AND THE ENEMY FORCES
ARE GROWING LARGER.
>> NO!
>> MASTER RIKUO?
I’M SORRY
I COULDN’T PROTECT YOU.
[ GASPS ]
[ GROWLS ]
>> WHAT IS THIS?
STAY BACK!
DON’T COME ANY CLOSER!
[ EXHALES ]
[ GROANS ]
>> WHO SAID THAT
YOU COULD EAT HER?
AH, THAT WAS GOOD.
NOW QUIT TRYING TO GO AFTER HER!
THIS GIRL IS MY BAIT!
[ PANTING ]
>> TSUCHI-GUMO!
>> WHY ISN’T HE HERE YET?
I’VE BEEN WAITING FOR AGES!
[ LAUGHS ]
I LIKE COMING ACROSS
INTERESTING GUYS LIKE HIM.
I’LL MAKE SURE TO COMPLETELY
DESTROY HIM WHEN HE GETS HERE!
>> HUH? HE’S COMING?
MASTER RIKUO IS COMING?
[ THINKING ]
HE’S ALIVE!
I CAN STILL PROTECT HIM!
>> I’VE GOT YOU HERE
AS BAIT, DON’T I?
SO SIT TIGHT AND BEHAVE!
>> I’M BAIT?
THAT MEANS HE’S USING ME
TO LURE MASTER RIKUO HERE!
WILL HE COME?
KNOWING MASTER RIKUO,
HE JUST MIGHT.
BECAUSE OF ME, HE’LL COME
TO TSUCHI-GUMO.
I CAN’T LET THAT HAPPEN.
I’M ONE OF HIS CLOSEST AIDES.
I HAVE TO GET AWAY SO THAT
I CAN PROTECT HIM!
>> FORGET IT!
[ GASPS ]
>> THERE’S NOTHING YOU CAN DO!
>> I CAN’T ESCAPE.
IF THAT’S THE CASE,
IF I’M GOING TO BE
A BURDEN TO MASTER RIKUO...
>> IT’S TIME.
LET’S GO.
>> HUH?
HOLD ON!
I FEEL SOMETHING BIG COMING.
>> HUH?
>> MASTER RIKUO...
[ SOBS ]
[ GASPS ]
IT’S MASTER RIKUO!
[ LAUGHS ]
>> SO YOU’RE FINALLY HERE!
>> I WAS TOO LATE.
>> HUH?
>> MASTER, WHY DID YOU HAVE
TO COME HERE?
I CAN’T PROTECT YOU ANYMORE!
[ GASPS ]
>> I CAME TO RESCUE YOU,
TSURARA.
I’M SORRY FOR
KEEPING YOU WAITING.
>> PRETTY COCKY
FOR SOMEONE SO SNEAKY.
>> GOOD TO SEE YOU.
I’M GONNA KILL YOU
FOR SURE THIS TIME.
>> I’VE BEEN WAITING FOR YOU.
IT’S BEEN SO LONG THAT
I WENT THROUGH 50 CASKS OF SAKE.
>> YOU STAY BACK.
>> HEY, WHAT’S YOUR NAME AGAIN?
RIKU SOMETHING...
RIKUO NURA.
[ LAUGHS ]
I HEARD THIS FROM KIDOMARU.
HE SAID YOU COULD ALTER
AWARENESS AND THAT’S HOW
YOU’VE DODGED MY ATTACKS.
I’VE NEVER COME ACROSS
A GUY LIKE YOU.
NOT ONLY THAT, I HEARD IT
WAS YOUR GRANDDAD WHO KILLED
HAGOROMO-GITSUNEH THE LAST TIME.
>> JUST SHUT UP AND FIGHT ME.
>> WE DON’T HAVE TO RUSH THINGS.
LET’S HAVE FUN WITH THIS.
WANT A DRINK?
IT’S GONNA BE A REAL PLEASURE
CRUSHING YOU.
[ GRUNTS ]
>> WELL, I GUESS I CAN’T
DODGE ALL OF THEM.
>> JUST DODGING ALL
MY ATTACKS WON’T DEFEAT ME!
HEY, YOU’RE IN THE WAY,
SO GET OUT OF HERE!
TELL YOUR GIRL TO TAKE OFF,
RIKUO, UNLESS YOU
WANT HER SMASHED UP.
>> MASTER RIKUO?
>> HUH?
>> PLEASE BACK AWAY.
I SWORE THAT I’D PROTECT YOU!
>> TSURARA, STOP!
>> I’M NOT BACKING DOWN!
I THOUGHT I LOST YOU BEFORE,
SO I CAN’T FAIL YOU AGAIN!
I DON’T WANT TO GO THROUGH
THAT HEARTACHE A SECOND TIME!
SO, PLEASE, LET ME FIGHT TOO!
MASTER, I’M BEGGING YOU!
PLEASE, MASTER RIKUO!
>> LISTEN!
YOU DON’T HAVE
TO PROTECT ME ANYMORE.
BUT YOU CAN STILL HELP ME
BY LENDING ME YOUR SPIRIT
AND YOUR STRENGTH.
I WANT YOU TO ENTRUST EVERYTHING
TO ME, YOUR HEART AND YOUR BODY.
>> HUH?
>> LET’S DO IT, TSURARA.
>> HOLD ON, MASTER...
>> GO ON.
>> MY HEART AND MY BODY?
>> SHOW ME YOUR FEAR.
>> BUT, MASTER RIKUO...
>> I SAID TO RELEASE YOUR FEAR,
TSURARA, FOR ME.
>> HUH? WHAT?
RIGHT!
HUH?
>> I HOPE YOU’RE READY.
HERE IT COMES, A SWORD
THAT’S ABLE TO REACH YOU!
>> YEAH? THIS OUGHT TO BE
INTERESTING THEN.
LET’S SEE THIS SWORD OF YOURS!
>> RIKUO!
>>THE SECOND HEIR’S
HIDDEN TECHNIQUE.
ONLY THOSE WHO POSSESS
BOTH HUMAN AND AYAKASHI BLOOD
CAN MASTER IT,
THE POWER TO DON
A HUNDRED DEMONS.
THIS ULTIMATE TECHNIQUE
INVOLVES TAKING THE FEAR
OF THOSE WHO SHARE
A MUTUAL TRUST WITH YOU
AND EQUIPPING IT.
>> TAKE THIS!
HUH? WHAT?
>> THE BUNDLING OF FEAR
MULTIPLIES ITS POWER.
WE CALLED IT THIS IN THE PAST,
THE HIDDEN TECHNIQUE OF
THE LORD OF A HUNDRED DEMONS,
EQUIP.
>> HUH?
>> EQUIP.
PINK BLOSSOMS UNDER THE SNOW.
>> GOOD ONE.
THAT’S AN INTERESTING TECHNIQUE
THERE!
>> YEAH, ISN’T IT?
THIS SWORD IS THE ONE
THAT REACHES YOU.
>> MASTER RIKUO?
WHAT’S GOING ON HERE?
HOLD ON.
WHAT WAS THAT?
[ GASP ]
WHAT ARE THOSE BIG TATTOOS
ON YOUR BACK?
>> PROOF OF EQUIP,
THAT WE FOUGHT SIDE BY SIDE.
>> EQUIP?
MASTER RIKUO, COULD THAT MEAN
THAT I WAS...THAT IS TO SAY,
DID I ACTUALLY HELP YOU OUT?
IS THAT WHAT YOU’RE GETTING AT?
>> OF COURSE, YOU DID!
AND I’M SURE I CAN
COUNT ON YOU AGAIN.
>> RIGHT!
>> HE DID IT!
>> HE GOT TSUCHI-GUMO’S ARM!
>> HE CAN WIN!
>> MASTER RIKUO CAN BEAT HIM!
>> I FINALLY FOUND ONE!
TO THINK YOU WERE ACTUALLY THIS
STRONG AND I WAS JUST KILLING
SOME TIME ’TIL I FOUGHT NUE TOO.
IT’S ALL GOOD, THOUGH.
SHOW ME THAT TECHNIQUE AGAIN.
THERE’S NO NEED TO HOLD BACK.
WHAT’S WRONG?
GO AHEAD AND DO IT!
[ STOMPING, SHOUTING ]
>> COME ON, RIKUO!
I’M THE ONE YOU’RE AFTER,
AREN’T I?
WHAT’S THE HOLDUP?
[ SHOUTING ]
>> LET’S HAVE SOME FUN HERE!
I’M STILL WAITING!
LET’S GET THE PARTY STARTED!
DON’T JUST STAND THERE!
YEAH!
IF I DON’T GET SERIOUS NOW,
I MIGHT LOSE MY LIFE
TO THAT SWORD OF YOURS!
ISN’T THAT RIGHT?
YEAH! YEAH! YEAH!
HURRY UP AND USE YOUR SWORD!
DO IT AGAIN AND
JUST KEEP IT COMING!
I FINALLY FOUND SOMEONE
WHO CAN FIGHT ME.
YEAH!
>> WHAT IS HE DOING?
RIKUO!
[ CRASHING ]
>> DON’T PASS OUT THIS TIME!
LET’S DO IT.
THE REAL FIGHT STARTS NOW!
MY FIRST ONE IN
A THOUSAND YEARS!
[ SHOUTING ]
>> GET READY, GET SET, YEAH!
>> YAH!
>> HE’S TOO FAST.
>> YOU GOT NOWHERE
TO RUN ANYMORE!
YEAH!
YEAH! YEAH!
IT LOOKS LIKE I HAVEN’T
CRUSHED YOU YET.
YOU REALLY KNOW HOW TO PUT ON
A GOOD SHOW.
HOWEVER, MY FEAR’S DONE ITS JOB.
YOUR NIGHT PARADE OF
A HUNDRED DEMONS
HAS FALLEN APART,
WHICH MEANS
YOU’RE ALL ALONE NOW.
HUH?
>> HE’S NOT ALONE!
>> WHAT THE--
>> I TOLD YOU, YOU CAN’T DESTROY
THEM UNLESS YOU KILL ME FIRST.
WE’RE GONNA MAKE SURE
TO CRUSH YOU.
>> HA!
WITH A NIGHT PARADE
THAT ONLY HAS THREE PEOPLE?
>> YOU’RE WRONG.
IT’S SIX.
ALL YOU HAVE TO DO
IS ASK, RIKUO.
AND WE TONO WILL LEND YOU
OUR STRENGTH.
>> DID YOU REALLY THINK
YOU WOULD LEAVE ALIVE,
NURARIHYON?
>> YES, WE ARE MOST
ASSUREDLY RUNNING OUT OF TIME.
>> IF YOU MESS UP,
I’LL KILL YOU.
>> IT’S BEEN A LONG TIME,
HAGOROMO-GITSUNEH.