>> HM?
THIS WASN’T THE ARRANGEMENT.
>> IT’S NOT THE TIME
WE AGREED ON YET.
>> AS A FAVOR TO YOU, THEN.
>> RIKUO, I THOUGHT
I MADE THINGS CLEAR.
I SAID THAT YOU HAD
TO ACCEPT YOUR HUMAN SIDE.
[ RUMBLING ]
>> I’M GOING TO DESTROY
ALL YOU KYOTO YOKAI!
>> WHAT IS THIS?
A SEAL?
>> BANISH INTO THE ABYSS!
YURA MAX!
>> YOU MUST BE HER,
THE JUTSU CASTER!
>> YURA MAX!
YURA MAX!
>> GODSPEED SLASH!
PLUM TREE!
[ GRUNTS ]
>> OH!
>> I SEE.
SO YOU’RE THE ONE.
>> LET ME GO!
>> I SHALL PRESENT YOUR LIVER
TO LADY HAGOROMO-GITSUNEH.
I’M SURE YOURS
WILL TASTE EXQUISITE.
>> GENGEN, RUN NOW!
[ GROWLING ]
>> WATER?
>> OH, WELL, GUESS
I WAS LITTLE LATE.
IT LOOKS LIKE MY TIMING
NEEDS SOME WORK.
[ COUGHING ]
>> THE BROKEN ARM DIDN’T HELP.
>> THAT WAS ON PURPOSE!
>> YOU KNOW, YURA,
THAT PERFORMANCE HAD ME
AT THE EDGE OF MY SEAT.
DO IT, MAMIRU.
USING YOUR ELECTRICITY
WITH OUR WATER.
YOU’VE PAID ATTENTION.
THERE’S NO NEED TO HOLD BACK.
DO IT!
THE SHIKIGAMI FUSION
OF US SIBLINGS.
>> AH!
>> HEY, YOU’RE GETTING YOUR ASS
HANDED TO YOU THERE, KIDOMARU!
>> I, KURATABO, WILL BE
YOUR OPPONENT NOW.
YOU ARE IN NO POSITION
TO WORRY ABOUT OTHERS.
>> YEAH?
>> IS THAT YOU, KAPPA?
>> I CAN’T HANDLE
THIS SANDY SOIL HERE!
KAPPA NINJA ART!
NINJA POND PASSAGE!
>> NOT SO FAST!
GET BACK HERE!
>> MIZUCHI BALLS!
BYE-BYE.
>> YOU’RE GOING, TOO!
[ SCREAMS ]
>> DID WE LOSE THEM?
>> KINO?
KINO, ARE YOU OKAY?
>> KUBINASHI?
>> OH, THANK GOODNESS
THAT YOU’RE ALL RIGHT!
[ CLEARS THROAT ]
>> HMM?
>> YOU’D BETTER THANK HER.
[ COUGHS ]
>> SHE HELPED US SAVE YOU,
AFTER ALL.
>> HUH?
>> THE ONMYOJI? I SEE.
THANKS FOR THAT.
>> IT WAS NOTHING.
YOU SAVED ME FROM KYUSO, RIGHT?
SO I GUESS WE’RE EVEN NOW.
>> YEAH, SURE.
>> THAT’S THE LAST TIME
THAT I’M SAVING A YOKAI!
>> NOW, NOW, YURA, DEAR.
>> WHAT?
>> WITHOUT US, THE SEALS
CAN’T BE RESTORED.
AND WITHOUT THEIR CLAN,
WE CAN’T DEFEAT THE KYOTO YOKAI.
[ GRUNTING ]
>> WE MUST FIGHT TOGETHER,
THE NURA CLAN
AND THE KEIKAIN,
AS WE DID IN THE PAST.
>> NUEH’S BIRTH IS NEARLY
UPON US NOW,
SO YOUR STRUGGLING
IS POINTLESS.
YET YOU STILL OPPOSE US!
>> HUH?
>> ZEN?
>> EASY, THERE.
YOUR BODY’S A REAL PIECE
OF WORK, RIKUO.
HOW IS IT THAT YOU’RE
STILL ALIVE AND KICKING?
>> THAT’S TRUE.
I NEVER REALLY THOUGHT ABOUT IT.
>> THERE ISN’T MUCH LEFT
FOR ME TO DO HERE.
MOVE IT!
>> HOLD ON, ZEN.
WHY ARE YOU HERE?
>> HUH?
BECAUSE WE’RE SWORN BROTHERS
WHO’VE EXCHANGED
CUPS OF LOYALTY.
TRAINING’S FINE,
BUT YOU SHOULD MAKE SURE
THAT YOUR BODY’S HEALED FIRST.
>> SORRY.
BECAUSE I’M SO WEAK, I’M BEING
A REAL BURDEN TO ALL OF YOU.
[ GRUNTS ]
>> THAT HURT!
WHAT ARE YOU DOING, ZEN?
>> WHAT THE HELL ARE YOU
TALKING ABOUT?
YOU’RE OUR LEADER, AREN’T YOU?
IF YOU WANT TO SAVE PEOPLE OR
GET SOME PAYBACK, GO AHEAD
AND DO WHATEVER IT TAKES.
YOU’RE THE ONE IN CHARGE.
>> BUT, ZEN...
>> PLUS, IF THEY DO
END UP TAKING POWER,
WE’LL ALL BE DEAD ANYWAY.
NO PRESSURE.
OOPS, I FORGOT.
GYUKI’S COMING BACK ONCE
THE SUN’S UP.
>> OH, HE IS, HUH?
THERE’S THIS TECHNIQUE
THAT GYUKI HAPPENED TO MENTION.
>> HUH?
>> BUT I THOUGHT THE ONLY
TECHNIQUES WERE INVOCATION
AND POSSESSION.
>> MY FAMILY FOLLOWED YOUR DAD
FOR GENERATIONS AS PART
OF THE NURA CLAN AND
I’D HEAR ALL THESE STORIES
ABOUT HIS HEROICS IN BATTLE,
HOW EVEN WEAK YOKAI
LIKE US WERE ABLE
TO HELP HIM AND
SPREAD OUR POISON WINGS.
>> GYUKI SAID BEFORE
THAT THE NIGHT PARADE’S
STRENGTH WOULD DEPEND ON MINE.
IF MY FEAR GETS STRONGER,
WILL IT TURN INTO
THAT TECHNIQUE?
>> RIKUO, TAKE A LOOK.
KEEP YOUR DISTANCE.
THEY MAY LOOK PRETTY,
BUT THEY’RE POISONOUS.
>> YEAH, I KNOW.
>> THIS IS THE TRAIT THAT’S
SHARED BY ALL ZEN YOKAI.
IT WOULDN’T BE A STRETCH
TO CALL IT MY FEAR
AND I WANT TO SPREAD THEM
OPEN, TOO.
I WANT TO USE MY WINGS
TO FIGHT FOR YOU.
AND SINCE WE’RE ON THAT,
I’M THE ONLY ONE
IN YOUR NIGHT PARADE
WHO’S HERE NOW.
SO I WANT TO FIGHT FOR YOU
OR OFFER YOU MY STRENGTH,
I’D SAY WE’RE DOING EXACTLY
WHAT GYUKI WAS BABBLING ABOUT,
WOULDN’T YOU?
>> I GUESS SO.
THANK YOU, ZEN.
[ THINKING ]
HE’S ENCOURAGING ME.
I KNOW HE’S WORRIED,
BUT IT’S STILL SO EMPOWERING.
JUST HAVING SOMEONE WHO BELIEVES
IN ME GIVES ME SO MUCH STRENGTH.
IT REALLY DOES.
AND THE STRENGTH I WANT IS
ALSO FOR EVERYONE’S SAKE.
>> HUH?
WHERE THE HELL DID THEY GO?
>> THEY RETREATED.
>> WE SHOULD BE ON OUR WAY
AS WELL.
WE SHOULDN’T BE
WASTING TIME LIKE THIS.
>> HMPH!
YOU AREN’T THE ONLY ONES HERE
WHO ARE SHORT ON TIME.
THOSE GUYS WERE SUCH A PAIN!
WE SHOULD HAVE
JUST AVOIDED THEM.
>> RYUJI?
I HAD HIM.
>> WELL, YOU SHOULD HAVE
FINISHED HIM OFF THEN!
>> YOU DIDN’T ORDER ME TO.
[ SIGH ]
>> IT’S LIKE TALKING
TO A GIANT BABY.
>> HUH?
>> I WONDER IF RIKUO’S COMING?
>> IT COULD BE THAT
HE’S ALREADY LONG GONE.
HE DID SEE LORD GYUKI
GET SERIOUS, AFTER ALL.
>> BUT THE REAL QUESTION
IS WHY THAT TENGU AGREED
TO HELP OUT WITH THE TRAINING.
I THOUGHT THE KYOTO YOKAI
WERE THE ENEMY.
>> THEY ARE.
IT’S WEIRD THAT LORD GYUKI’S
WORKING WITH ONE.
>> HM?
[ FOOTSTEPS APPROACHING ]
>> GYUKI, LET’S CONTINUE THIS.
>> IT’S MORNING.
>> OH?
GUESS SO.
>> WE ONLY FENDED OFF
THOSE INSECT YOKAI
DUE TO YOUR DECISIVE BLOW.
THANK YOU.
I’M GRATEFUL.
>> SURE THING.
[ PANTING ]
>> WHAT HAPPENED HERE?
AKIFUSA, TELL ME JUST
WHAT WENT ON HERE!
GRANDPA!
>> IT’S YOU, YURA.
YOU’RE STILL SAFE.
THANK GOODNESS.
COME HERE.
I’D LIKE TO SEE YOU
A LITTLE CLOSER.
[ GASPING ]
>> GRANDPA, YOU HAVE TO HOLD ON!
>> YURA, DID YOU EVER
LEARN THE UHO STEP?
>> GRANDPA, I MASTERED
THAT A FEW YEARS AGO.
>> YURA?
>> WHAT IS IT?
JUST TELL ME.
>> I THINK OF YOU AS A CRYSTAL.
YOU’RE THE ONE THAT HOLDS
THE FUTURE OF THE KEIKAIN CLAN
WITHIN YOU, ONE THAT SHINES
SO BRIGHT THAT IT BLINDS
MY OLD EYES.
YOU ARE OUR MOST
PRECIOUS CRYSTAL, YURA.
>> WHAT ARE YOU TALKING ABOUT?
YOU’RE MORE IMPORTANT THAN ME!
>> YOU’RE SO VERY STRONG.
WHEN I LOOK AT YOU,
I’M FILLED WITH SUCH
OPTIMISM AND HOPE FOR
OUR CLAN’S FUTURE.
YURA, PLEASE GROW EVEN STRONGER.
YOU HAVE TO BECOME
MUCH STRONGER THAN YOU ARE.
PLEASE DO SO IN OUR PLACE.
YURA, PROTECT THE PEOPLE.
>> NO!
WAKE UP, PLEASE, GRANDPA!
DON’T GO!
GRANDPA!
[ CRYING ]
>> SHE’S ASLEEP.
>> WHO COULD BLAME HER?
THE POOR THING’S EXHAUSTED.
SHE WAS FIGHTING DAY AND NIGHT.
>> IT SEEMS THE KEIKAIN CLAN
HAS GROWN CONSIDERABLY WEAKER
THESE 400 YEARS.
IT SHOULD COME AS NO SURPRISE,
AS THE CLAN HASN’T FOUGHT
ANY REAL BATTLES UNTIL
HAGOROMO-GITSUNEH HAS RETURNED.
HUMANKIND AND ORGANIZATIONS
CAN ONLY SEE REALITY
WHEN IN THE FACE OF DANGER.
SO FOOLISH.
>> THE MAIN THING IS
THAT YOU REALIZE THAT.
AS LONG AS GUYS LIKE YOU
ARE AROUND, THINGS WILL BE
ALL RIGHT.
IT’S NOT LIKE I REALLY CARE,
THOUGH.
AND, ANYWAY, YOU’VE GOT
THAT LITTLE GIRL THERE
AND THOSE TWO IN BLACK
TO HELP YOU OUT.
>> I SUPPOSE THAT’S TRUE.
I’M SORRY.
IT SEEMS I’VE EVEN
WORRIED A YOKAI.
>> HA!
>> THE 13th HEIR?
>> WELL, NOW WHAT SHALL I DO?
IT APPEARS THAT I’LL HAVE
TO LEAVE THINGS IN
YOUR HANDS, AKIFUSA.
>> OH, THAT WOUND’S
STILL ACHING.
>> ARE YOU ALL RIGHT?
>> YOU TWO SHOULD REST
WHILE YOU CAN.
TSUCHI-GUMO GAVE YOU
QUITE A BEATING
AND ANOTHER SUICIDE CHARGE
WILL END WITH SIMILAR RESULTS.
REST, YURA, DEAR.
IT’S NEARLY OVER NOW.
PLEASE DON’T HESITATE
TO SUMMON ME.
>> HE JUST VANISHED.
>> SO HE WAS A SPIRIT AFTER ALL.
>> DON’T GO, GRANDPA.
PLEASE DON’T GO.
[ SNARLING ]
>> NURARIHYON’S FEAR,
IT DISTORTS
HIS FOE’S PERCEPTIONS
AND CUTS THEIR FEAR.
BUT THAT ALONE ISN’T
ENOUGH TO DEFEAT TSUCHI-GUMO.
YOU’VE TAKEN ON YOUR NIGHT FORM.
LET’S MOVE ON THEN.
YOU DO WANT IT, DON’T YOU?
A BLADE THAT WILL
REACH A POWERFUL FOE?
THERE’S NO TIME LEFT.
YOU MUST THINK OF NOTHING ELSE!
>> ANOTHER NIGHT’S
COME AND GONE.
YOU SHOULD SEE THE LOOK ON
YOUR FACE RIGHT NOW, RIKUO.
I HEAR THIS PLACE
IS KNOWN AS MT. KURAMA.
IT’S THE LEGENDARY PLACE
WHERE KURAMA TENGU TRAINED
USHIWAKAMARU, BETTER KNOWN
AS YOSHITSUNE MINAMOTO.
>> SECONDS!
>> HURRY IT UP!
>> HEY, NO ONE INVITED
YOU GUYS TO EAT WITH US!
>> I HEARD YOU DID CHORES
IN TONO ALONG WITH TRAINING.
IF YOU’RE TRAINING TOMORROW,
DO THE COOKING, TOO.
>> A BLADE THAT
REACHES TSUCHI-GUMO.
DO I HAVE IT IN ME?
I CAN’T WIN WITHOUT IT.
>> THAT’S ALL YOU’VE BEEN
SAYING FOR HOURS.
GYUKI DOESN’T SHOW ANY MERCY,
THOUGH.
ANYWAY, REST UP.
YOU’RE GONNA FIGHT HIM IN
YOUR DAY FORM WHEN
THE SUN’S UP, RIGHT?
[ WIND BLOWING ]
>> WHAT THE HELL?
[ GROWLING ]
>> HEY, GIVE HIM
SOME TIME BEFORE
YOU START IT UP AGAIN, GYUKI!
>> YEAH! HOLD ON!
AND WHY ARE YOU DRAGGING US
INTO IT?
>> ZEN, COME ON!
THIS WAY!
>> WHAT’S GOING ON HERE?
GYUKI’S HARDLY GIVING YOU
ANY TIME AT ALL TO REST!
>> JUST STAY BACK.
THESE GUYS ARE SERIOUSLY
TRYING TO KILL US.
>> THEY’RE WHAT?
[ GASPS ]
>> SO, GYUKI, IS THAT BRAT
MAKING ANY PROGRESS?
>> I’M LETTING HIM REST A WHILE.
WE’LL RESUME SHORTLY.
>> I SEE.
SHE’LL GIVE BIRTH SOON.
THE REINCARNATION YOKAI
REBORN SEVEN TIMES
IN SIX CENTURIES.
WHEN HAGOROMA-GITSUNEH GOT
HER NINTH TAIL, I LOST MY PLACE.
IT WAS MINAGOROSHI-JIZO
WHO TOOK MY SPOT.
HE TAMPERED WITH THE MEMORIES
OF SOME OF THE KYOTO YOKAI
AND STOLE MY POSITION
FROM RIGHT UNDER ME
USING A STRANGE POWER TO DO IT.
>> COULD THIS MINAGOROSHI-JIZO
YOU SPEAK OF HAVE BEWITCHED
HAGOROMO-GITSUNEH TOO?
>> NO, I DOUBT THAT.
NO AYAKASHI COULD MANIPULATE
HAGOROMO-GITSUNEH.
I DON’T KNOW WHAT HE’S THINKING,
BUT HE PROBABLY WANTS
AN ADVANTAGEOUS POSITION
AFTER THE BIRTH.
>> SO YOU REALLY DON’T KNOW
WHAT HE’S AFTER?
>> BUT WHAT I AM CERTAIN OF
IS THAT I’LL MAKE HIM REGRET
HOW HE TREATED ME,
THE GREAT TENGU OF MT. KARUMA!
THIS UPCOMING BIRTH
THAT HE’S PLANNED IS SOMETHING
THAT I’LL NEVER ACCEPT!
I WILL STOP IT AT ANY COST!
>> I KNOW.
I’M SURE RIKUO WILL GAIN
THE NECESSARY POWER
TO DO JUST THAT
AND I’M GRATEFUL
FOR ALL YOUR HELP.
IT WON’T BE LONG NOW.
>> IS THAT RIGHT?
BUT, GYUKI, THE TIME LIMIT
THAT WE BOTH AGREED ON
IS JUST ABOUT HERE NOW AND,
SINCE IT IS, WE’LL DO THIS
ON OUR OWN!
WE’LL BE TAKING
THE NENEKIRIMARU NOW.
>> WHAT?
[ SHOUTS ]
>> GOZUMARU!
>> BASTARDS!
>> HEY, YOU’RE GONNA PAY
FOR HURTING HIM!
>> STAY BACK!
I’LL CREATE AN OPENING
FOR YOU THREE,
SO USE IT TO GET OUT OF HERE!
>> HEY, QUIT IT, RIKUO!
[ SHOUTING ]
>> MOVE IT!
>> RIGHT!
>> YOU TOO, ZEN!
>> WOULD YOU QUIT IT ALREADY?
>> QUIT WHAT?
>> YOU KNOW EXACTLY WHAT.
YOU’RE TREATING ME
LIKE I’M A BURDEN HERE.
>> HUH?
NO, I’M NOT!
>> YES, YOU ARE!
>> OH, YEAH? HOW?
>> IT’S CLEAR AS DAY!
>> WOULD YOU JUST GO?
>> WHAT?
NO WAY IN HELL!
>> JUST DO IT!
>> THERE’S NO WAY RIKUO CAN WIN
AGAINST THE KURAMA TENGU.
IT’S TRUE HE GRASPED
THE ESSENCE OF NURARIHYON
AND TONO AND THAT HE WAS ABLE
TO DISTORT PERCEPTIONS
WITH THAT FEAR AND
AVOID A FATAL INJURY IN
THE BATTLE WITH TSUCHI-GUMO.
BUT HE HASN’T YET BEEN ABLE
TO DISCOVER HIS OWN SELF.
HE’S FORGOTTEN
HOW ADAPTABLE HUMANS ARE.
[ SHOUTS ]
>> ALL RIGHT, THEN.
JUST STAY BACK!
I’LL BEAT THEM!
>> I WAS ONCE HUMAN, TOO,
SO I UNDERSTAND WHY RIKUO TRIES
TO HIDE HIS HUMAN WEAKNESS
FROM THOSE AROUND HIM.
BUT THE SECOND HEIR
WAS DIFFERENT.
HE WAS ABLE TO TRUST
HIS PEOPLE AND DEPEND ON THEM.
HE ACCEPTED HIS HUMAN SIDE
AND ACCOMPLISHED THINGS
ONLY A HUMAN COULD DO.
>> I’M HALF HUMAN, SO I FIGURED
THE SMARTEST THING THAT I CAN DO
IS RELY ON ALL YOU YOKAI.
BUT I WANT TO FIGHT SIDE
BY SIDE, SO, PLEASE,
WHAT I COULD REALLY USE
IS YOUR STRENGTH. LEND IT TO ME.
>> THAT TECHNIQUE ALLOWS AN
ALREADY FORMIDABLE FEAR TO EQUIP
A GREATER FEAR, A TECHNIQUE
WORTHY OF A NIGHT PARADE’S LORD.
>> DAMN IT!
THESE BASTARDS ARE
REALLY STRONG!
I CAN’T DRIVE THEM OFF!
I WANT A SWORD THAT
CAN PROTECT ZEN.
[ CRASHING ]
>> RIKUO, I WON’T STAND BACK
AND WON’T RUN AWAY.
ALL I WANT IS TO BE
USEFUL TO YOU.
I THOUGHT I WAS IN YOUR NIGHT
PARADE OF A HUNDRED DEMONS!
>> ZEN, HELP ME OUT THEN
AND QUIT BUGGING ME ABOUT IT.
>> AS LONG AS IT’S CLEAR.
>> GO AHEAD AND SPREAD
THOSE POISON WINGS FOR ME.
>> WITH PLEASURE, YOUNG MASTER!
[ GASPS ]
>> RIKUO, SEE IT!
YOU CAN BECOME MUCH STRONGER!
>> IF YOU DON’T SHOW UP,
THEN WE’LL KILL TSUCHI-GUMO!
>> I CAN’T PROTECT YOU ANYMORE!
[ LAUGHS ]
>> I’LL MAKE SURE TO COMPLETELY
DESTROY HIM WHEN HE GETS HERE!
>> I CAME TO RESCUE YOU.