>> SEIMEI!
[ SHOUTS ]
IT’S BEEN A THOUSAND YEARS
SINCE I LAST FOUGHT YOU!
[ GROWLING ]
>> WHAT?
>> HMM. A FAMILIAR FACE, I SEE.
DESTROY!
[ GRUNTS ]
[ SCREAMS ]
>> NO WAY!
>> WHAT?
>> TSUCHI-GUMO’S...
[ SCREAMING ]
>> DAMN IT, SEIMEI!
YOU AND I STILL HAVE
A SCORE TO SETTLE HERE!
>> LORD SEIMEI, I BROUGHT
THE SWORD AS I PROMISED
ALL THOSE YEARS AGO.
>> THIS CITY HAS BECOME FILTHY
OVER THESE LAST CENTURIES.
IT’S NOT A FITTING HOME
FOR US, NOT ANYMORE.
[ LAUGHING ]
[ GASPING ]
>> DAMN IT!
>> I MUST ONCE AGAIN
BUILD IT ANEW.
>> WHAT IS THIS GUY?
>> HIS POWER’S INSANE!
>> THIS IS AN EXCELLENT SWORD,
ADMIRABLY DONE,
SANMOTO GOROZAEMON.
>> SANMOTO GOROZAEMON?
>> NO! IT CAN’T BE!
>> THAT GUY’S
SANMOTO GOROZAEMON?
>> I’VE NEVER HEARD OF HIM.
WHO IS HE?
>> A YOKAI FROM EDO
AND HE WAS ONCE
OUR GREATEST ENEMY.
HE WAS THE LEADER OF
THE HUNDRED TALES CLAN.
THE SECOND HEIR
DESTROYED HIM SEVERAL YEARS AGO.
>> EDO’S HUNDRED TALES CLAN?
>> SO HE WAS THE ONE
PULLING ALL THE STRINGS?
[ GASPING ]
>> WHAT’S GOING ON HERE?
>> LORD SEIMEI,
I AM SANMOTO’S EYE.
>> HMM.
>> PLEASE CALL ME
MINAGOROSHI-JIZO IN THIS FORM.
SANMOTO IS SPLIT
INTO 100 BODY PARTS,
SO THINGS CAN GET
GET CONFUSING.
[ LAUGHS ]
AND WE WOULDN’T WANT
THOSE FOOLS TO BE FREED
FROM MY BRAINWASHING
JUST YET.
[ LAUGHING ]
>> BRAINWASHED?
WHICH FOOLS?
>> TRANSFORMING THIS CITY
WILL COME FIRST.
AND BEYOND THAT LIES
THE WORLD THAT I DESIRE.
>> BURN! BURN!
MY GREAT AMBITION HAS BEEN
REALIZED AT LONG LAST!
EVERY AYAKASHI AND HUMAN
WILL KNEEL BEFORE US NOW!
>> DAMN YOU!
>> HUH?
[ GASPS ]
[ GRUNTS ]
>> JUST ACCEPT YOUR DEFEAT!
[ SCREECHES ]
[ GROANS ]
>> GIVEN LORD SEIMEI’S POWER,
THE ONMYOJI AND THE NURA CLAN
ARE HARDLY WORTHY ADVERSARIES.
RIHAN NURA MET HIS END SWIFTLY
AND YOU’RE ALL EVEN
WEAKER THAN HE WAS.
[ LAUGHS ]
OUR GRUDGE HAS SMOLDERED
FOR CENTURIES AND NOW
FLAMES HAVE BEEN FANNED
THAT WILL REDUCE ALL HUMANS
AND THE ACCURSED NURA CLAN
TO ASHES ALONGSIDE THIS CITY--
>> MISS KEIKAIN!
>> --THAT ONCE STOOD
AS YOUR CAPITAL.
NOW YOU CAN BURN
FOR ALL ETERNITY!
[ GRUNTS ]
WHAT THE HELL IS GOING ON HERE?
IT CAN’T BE!
NOT WHEN I’VE JUST WON THIS!
MY YOKAI AURA IS DISSIPATING!
>> SO YOU WERE BEHIND IT ALL.
YOU KILLED MY...
[ COUGHS ]
>> THANKS, NURA.
>> HMM?
>> YOU BASTARD!
WHAT ARE YOU UP TO?
YOU MANIPULATED YOUR OWN MOTHER
AND YOU WERE TOYING AROUND
WITH US.
>> MASTER RIKUO!
>> YOU’VE BEEN DEAD FOR
A THOUSAND YEARS, SO DON’T GO
MESSING AROUND WITH THE WORLD.
>> WHO ARE YOU?
>> GO BACK TO HELL!
[ SHOUTS ]
>> NO!
DON’T DO IT, MASTER!
>> WHAT ARE YOU DOING?
WEREN’T YOU JUST WATCHING?
>> YOU CAN’T BEAT HIM ALONE!
>> NURA WILL GET HIMSELF
DESTROYED!
>> MASTER RIKUO!
>> WHAT THE HELL?
>> INTRIGUING, NENEKIRIMARU.
IT IS INDEED A FINE SWORD.
HOWEVER, IT’S NOT QUITE POWERFUL
ENOUGH TO BE MY DOWNFALL.
>> NENEKIRIMARU!
[ GASPING ]
>> SO YOU’RE RIHAN’S
REAL SON, ARE YOU?
YOU’RE NOT STRONG ENOUGH.
>> RIKUO!
DAMN IT!
[ GRUNTS ]
>> HOW PATHETIC.
THOSE FALSE MEMORIES
GAVE BIRTH TO PITY.
>> ARE YOU CRAZY?
WHAT THE HELL ARE YOU DOING?
>> RIKUO.
>> GRAMPS!
>> HEY, GUYS.
BUY ME A LITTLE TIME, WILL YOU?
THERE’S SOMETHING THAT I HAVE
TO CHECK OUT, SO KEEP HIM BUSY.
>> YES, SIR.
THE MOST POWERFUL
ONMYOJI RESURRECTED.
>> LIKE IT’S GONNA BE THAT EASY.
OUR COMMANDER’S A RIOT.
>> RIKUO!
>> ARE YOU OKAY?
>> WHAT WERE YOU THINKING?
>> HEY, GRAMPS.
I WAS THINKING COULD SHE
BE MAYBE MY LONG-LOST SISTER?
>> HUH?
>> NO.
THAT’S NOT WHAT IT IS, RIKUO.
I THINK THIS SCHEME OF THEIRS
GOES EVEN DEEPER THAN THAT.
>> BUT...
[ GIGGLING ]
[ SCREAM ]
>> FATHER?
>> WHY DID SHE
SAY THAT BACK THERE?
>> SHE’S THE SPITTING IMAGE
OF HER.
I MEAN, YAMABUKI-OTOME,
AN AYAKASHI WHO WAS
ONCE RIHAN’S WIFE.
THIS WAS BACK SEVERAL
CENTURIES AGO WHEN PRINCESS YO,
YOUR GRANDMOTHER,
WAS STILL ALIVE.
AND THAT YOUNG WOMAN MARRIED
INTO THE NURA CLAN
AND LIVED ON OUR ESTATE.
>> DAD, YOU KNOW, I’M THINKING
OF MARRYING THIS GIRL.
>> HUH?
SLOW DOWN, RIHAN.
JUST WHERE DID YOU
PICK HER UP FROM?
>> WHY?
IT’S MY LOVE LIFE.
I DON’T HAVE TO TELL YOU
A THING.
>> DAMN IT!
I’M YOUR FATHER, RIHAN!
>> HUH?
>> HEY, YOU! ARE YOU SURE?
I’M WARNING YOU.
BEING HIS WIFE WON’T BE EASY.
>> I AM.
MY NAME’S YAMABUKI-OTOME.
I AM UNWORTHY,
BUT I HOPE THAT...
>> SHE WAS AN EXTREMELY
GRACEFUL AND BEAUTIFUL AYAKASHI.
THAT’S WHEN RIHAN’S GLORY DAYS
BEGAN, AND THOSE DAYS LASTED
A LONG, LONG WHILE.
THINGS STAYED THE SAME.
IRONICALLY, I THINK THOSE TIMES
MIGHT HAVE BEEN HARD ON HER.
>> WHAT?
>> BECAUSE OF THE FOX’S CURSE
CAST ON ME, OUR FAMILY WASN’T
ABLE TO CONTINUE ITS LINE.
>> BUT WHAT ABOUT DAD AND ME?
WE STILL WERE BORN.
>> YOU’RE CHILDREN OF
AN AYAKASHI AND A HUMAN.
THE FOX’S CURSE HADN’T
COUNTED ON THAT POSSIBILITY.
>> HOW LONG WILL IT TAKE
FOR HER TO GIVE US AN HEIR?
>> IT’S ALREADY BEEN 50 YEARS.
>> SHE BLAMED HERSELF FOR NOT
BEING ABLE TO GIVE BIRTH
TO AN HEIR.
SHE DISAPPEARED ONE DAY
LEAVING BEHIND A BRANCH
OF YAMABUKI ROSES
AND NEXT TO IT WAS A POEM.
>> OTOME...
>> SEVENFOLD, EIGHTFOLD,
THE YAMABUKI ROSE BLOOMS,
BUT NOT A SINGLE FRUIT
IT BEARS.
SUCH SADNESS.
>> SHE COULD MAKE FLOWERS
BLOOM BEAUTIFULLY,
BUT WAS UNABLE
TO CONCEIVE ONE HERSELF.
>> I NEVER KNEW THAT.
>> EVEN NOW, ONLY THE TOP CLAN
OFFICIALS KNOW THIS.
AS FOR WHAT HAPPENED TO HER
IN THE END,
NO ONE EVER FOUND OUT.
>> I...
I HAD DECIDED
TO LEAVE THIS WORLD
SO I COULD AT LAST WITHER AWAY.
>> YOU’RE AWAKE!
>> AND WITHIN THAT
PITCH-BLACK WORLD,
I COULD HEAR A MAN’S VOICE.
>> IS THIS HER?
SHE SEEMS TO BE AN AYAKASHI.
SHE WAS ORIGINALLY HUMAN.
PERFECT.
>> THAT’S IT!
THE SOUL REBIRTH!
THEN YOU REALLY ARE
YAMABUKI-OTOME?
[ CHUCKLES ]
>> DAMN IT!
THE NURA CLAN AGAIN!
RIHAN NURA, HE MANAGED
TO SMASH MY SIDE THIS TIME.
>> THE TOKUGAWA’S END,
THE MEIJI ERA
DURING THE WAR AND AFTER.
MY MOTHER SHOULD HAVE
APPEARED NUMEROUS TIMES
WHEN THE WORLD
WAS SHROUDED IN DARKNESS,
BUT EACH TIME HE PREVENTED IT.
I CANNOT BE REVIVED UNLESS
RIHAN NURA IS KILLED.
>> I AGREE, AND I HAVE
TO GET REVENGE,
NO MATTER WHAT THE COST,
REVENGE FOR MY HUNDRED
TALES CLAN WHICH SHOULD
RIGHTFULLY RULE EDO.
>> SO, WHAT TO DO?
>> GREAT OR NOT, ALL PREY
LET DOWN THEIR GUARD
AT SOME POINT.
THAT’S THE ANSWER.
EVERY MAN HAS A WEAKNESS
FOR HIS DAUGHTER.
>> DAUGHTER?
HE HAS NO SUCH CHILDREN.
>> BUT RIHAN DID FALL
IN LOVE ONCE,
AN AYAKASHI WHO EVENTUALLY
BECAME HIS WIFE.
>> I SEE.
I TAKE IT THAT YOU’RE GOING
TO FABRICATE THIS GIRL.
BUT EVEN WITH
YOUR ILLUSION JUTSU,
WE’RE SPEAKING
ABOUT RIHAN NURA.
>> AND THAT’S EXACTLY WHY
YOUR SOUL REBIRTH JUTSU IS
SO NECESSARY FOR US TO SUCCEED.
>> I BROUGHT YAMABUKI-OTOME
BACK TO LIFE WITH MY JUTSU
AND SANMOTO IMPLANTED
FALSE MEMORIES OF
BEING RIHAN’S DAUGHTER
WITHIN HER MIND,
MURDERING RIHAN NURA
AND THEN BECOMING THE VESSEL
FOR MY MOTHER’S REBIRTH.
SHE FULFILLED
BOTH HER TASKS ADMIRABLY.
>> I’VE HEARD ENOUGH OF THIS!
YOU’LL PAY!
>> WE SHALL ATTACK TOGETHER!
[ SHOUTING ]
[ SHOUTING, GRUNTING ]
>> IT WAS RIGHT
AFTER I HEARD THAT MAN’S VOICE
THAT I NOTICED WHAT HAPPENED.
I HAD BECOME A YOUNG GIRL.
WOULD YOU LIKE TO PLAY?
FALSE MEMORIES
WERE PLANTED WITHIN ME.
COME ON.
>> OKAY.
>> RIKUO, WHO’S SHE?
>> DAD?
>> HELLO, FATHER.
>> IT’S OKAY, DAD.
SHE WAS JUST PLAYING WITH ME.
>> MASTER RIHAN
WAS HESITANT AT FIRST.
EVENTUALLY, HE TOOK MY HAND
IN HIS.
I WAS SO HAPPY THAT DAY...
[ LAUGHTER ]
SO VERY HAPPY, MORE THAN
I EVER THOUGHT POSSIBLE.
[ CACKLES ]
>> OH, WHAT’S THAT OVER THERE?
>> DON’T STRAY TOO FAR, RIKUO.
[ LAUGHS ]
>> YAMABUKI?
>> OH, HOW PRETTY.
>> SEVENFOLD, EIGHTFOLD,
THE YAMABUKI ROSE BLOOMS,
BUT NOT A SINGLE FRUIT IT BEARS.
SUCH SADNESS.
THEY REPRESENT
MANY THINGS LIKE GRACE,
DECENCY AND EVEN LONGING.
IT’S LIKE YOU’RE ALMOST
THE DAUGHTER WE NEVER HAD.
[ GRUNTS ]
>> HEY, DAD!
>> RIKUO.
>> THE POEM MASTER RIHAN
RECITED WAS THE TRIGGER.
>> NO...
>> THAT WAS WHEN...
>> MASTER RIHAN!
>> I WAS MADE
TO REMEMBER EVERYTHING.
[ SCREAMS ]
>> NO! DON’T DIE!
MASTER RIHAN!
[ LAUGHING ]
>> YES, MOURN OVER HIM, WOMAN.
HE WAS THE MAN THAT YOU LOVED
AND YOU JUST KILLED HIM
WHILE PRETENDING TO BE
THE CHILD YOU COULDN’T CONCEIVE!
[ LAUGHING ]
>> YES, I HAVE
RESTLESSLY WAITED.
>> WHO ARE YOU, LADY?
>> MY LOVE DIED BY MY OWN HAND.
THAT WAS WHEN I TURNED
INTO THAT FOX.
>> THE SOUL REBIRTH,
IT WAS SEIMEI’S TRICKERY.
HE USED A YOKAI
WHO WAS ONCE HUMAN,
REVIVING HER AS A VESSEL
FOR HAGOROMO-GITSUNE.
>> HUH?
>> THE SITUATION WAS PERFECT
FOR THE MASTERMIND
WHO CONSIDERED MY FRIEND
NURARIHYON’S SON
A GREAT NUISANCE.
>> HIDEMOTO.
>> DAMN IT!
EVEN WITH ALL OF US HERE,
WE COULDN’T GIVE THIS GUY
A SCRATCH,
NOT EVEN A LITTLE ONE!
>> I DOUBT THAT IT’S
JUST OUR AGE.
>> YOU BETTER NOT DO
ANYTHING RECKLESS, GYUKI.
>> RECKLESS?
THAT’S THE DEFINITION OF
THE NURA CLAN.
>> HOW UNPLEASANT.
[ GRUNTS ]
>> RIKUO?
>> I’M SORRY.
I KEPT YOU WAITING.
LET’S FINISH THIS NOW.
WHAT DO YOU SAY?
>> FINISH IT?
THERE’S STILL SO MUCH TO DO.
WE’VE JUST NOW STARTED.
I’LL DESTROY THIS DISORDERLY
WORLD WHERE HUMANS
AND AYAKASHI COMMINGLE
AND A WORLD WHERE
THE DARKNESS RULES
OVER THE LIGHT
WILL TAKE ITS PLACE.
>> WEREN’T YOU HUMAN ONCE, TOO?
>> OLD MAN.
>> AFTER A THOUSAND YEARS,
I WAS AT LAST
RESURRECTED IN THIS WAY.
I HAVE OUTGROWN THE NEED FOR
A HUMAN VESSEL AND NOW STAND
AT THE VERY PINNACLE
OF DARKNESS.
>> SO YOU’VE GOT NO DOUBTS
OR REGRETS ABOUT
LOSING YOUR HUMANITY?
WELL, IN MY MIND,
WHILE THEY’RE CLUMSY
AND TROUBLESOME,
MY SON AND GRANDSON
WHO ARE HUMAN AND AYAKASHI
ARE MY PRIDE AND JOY.
>> HOW NICE FOR YOU.
THREE GENERATIONS OF NURARIHYON,
BUT YOUR BLOODLINE WILL NEVER
KNOW WHAT’S STARTING HERE.
AS REQUESTED, I’LL FINISH THIS.
>> MASTER!
>> TSURARA!
>> LET’S GO, RIKUO.
>> YOU BET.
[ EXHALES ]
>> LET’S FOCUS ON
CONTAINING HIM!
>> GOT IT!
>> YOU’RE WIDE OPEN, BASTARD!
WHAT THE...?
NOT AGAIN!
JAMI?
THAT’S YOUR NAME, RIGHT?
[ GRUNTS ]
>> LET’S GO, AO!
>> RIGHT!
>> THEY ALL MISSED THE MARK!
>> IT’S NOT EVEN CHILD’S PLAY.
[ SHOUTING ]
[ EXPLOSION ]
>> HUH?
>> COME ON, GUYS.
LET’S GO.
YOU’RE MY NIGHT PARADE,
SO RELEASE YOUR FEAR NOW
AND ENTRUST IT...
ALL TO ME.
>> NURA CLAN, EVEN WITH
RIHAN NURA DEAD,
YOU STILL CONTINUE
TO GET IN MY WAY.
>> I’LL SHOW YOU, ABE NO SEIMEI.
THIS IS MY NIGHT PARADE
OF A HUNDRED DEMONS!