>> ALL THE STRONG CHALLENGERS
I WANTED ARE IN ONE SPOT.
>> [ GASP ]
>> HUH?
>> WHAT IS THAT?
>> AAH!
>> WHO IS THIS GUY?
LOOK OUT! HE’S COMING!
>> WHERE DID HE COME FROM?
>> THIS GUY’S ONE OF THEM!
STAY BACK IF YOU CAN’T
HANDLE THIS!
>> THE NAME IS TSUCHI-GUMO.
I CAME HERE LOOKING FOR
STRONG YOKAI TO FIGHT.
SO WHO’S UP FOR IT?
SOME OF YOU HERE HAVE GOT TO
HAVE A LITTLE BACKBONE IN YOU.
IS IT YOU?
MAYBE YOU?
OR IS IT YOU GUYS?
I FIGHT WOMEN, TOO.
I DON’T REALLY CARE AS LONG
AS SOMEONE FIGHTS ME.
>> YOU BASTARD!
>> DON’T MOCK US!
>> STAY BACK AND DON’T BUTT IN!
I’LL FIGHT HIM!
[ SINGING IN JAPANESE ]
>> NIJO CASTLE.
>> AH, THERE AREN’T MANY BABES
AROUND HERE.
>> YEAH.
>> LOOK, GUYS!
>> SHE’S BLACK FROM HEAD TO TOE.
>> AND SHE’S A HOTTIE!
>> TO THINK THAT VISITORS
WOULD STILL BE HERE.
>> OH, YOU MEAN BECAUSE IT’S
ALMOST CLOSING TIME, RIGHT?
>> YOU A LOCAL
OR ON A SCHOOL TRIP?
IT’S WEIRD THAT YOU’RE ALONE,
THOUGH.
ARE YOU A HISTORY BUFF
OR SOMETHING?
YEAH, THAT’S IT, RIGHT?
>> IT’S DANGEROUS AT NIGHT
THESE DAYS.
WHY DON’T YOU HANG OUT WITH US.
>> HUMANS WHO CANNOT GRASP
MY FEAR OR EVEN SEE MY HUNDRED
DEMONS ARE BETTER DEAD.
>> YES, MY LADY.
IT WOULD SEEM THAT THE ONMYOJI
AREN’T HERE AT NIJO CASTLE,
OR TSUCHI-GUMO.
>> WHAT? HE’S NOT?
KYOTO’S CONQUEST IS AT HAND.
WE SHOULD ALL BE HERE TO SEE IT.
HUH. HE’S A CAPRICIOUS ONE.
I WONDER WHAT HE COULD BE UP TO.
NO MATTER.
WE’VE WAITED LONG ENOUGH.
LET US ENTER MY NEW CASTLE.
>> I HAVEN’T DESTROYED
A NIGHT PARADE IN 400 YEARS.
NOBODY HERE REALLY STOOD OUT,
BUT IT WAS STILL FUN.
HUH?
YOU!
YOU’RE THE COWARD WHO SEALED ME
AWAY 400 YEARS AGO.
TELL ME, ARE YOU HERE
TO TRY AND SEAL ME AGAIN?
>> YOU STOOD FIRM, MY MASTER,
AS DID RYUJI BY SHIELDING HER.
>> DAMN!
>> BIG BROTHER!
>> HOPEFULLY, HIS LEGS
ARE STILL WHOLE.
WE HAVE TO FLEE SOMEHOW.
HIS ARRIVAL WAS INAUSPICIOUS.
WE MUST NOT ENGAGE TSUCHI-GUMO.
HE IS ONE WE MUST AVOID.
>> AN AYAKASHI WE MUST AVOID?
>> STANDING UP AGAIN, HUH?
SEEMS YOU GUYS HAVE GUTS!
FINE, THEN!
LET’S HAVE SOME FUN!
>> STAND FIRM!
HE’S HEADED THIS WAY!
YOU SHOULD TAKE THINGS EASY.
YOU WERE INJURED
IN YOUR LAST BATTLE.
>> SO? NOT YOUR PROBLEM.
>> NO. STAND DOWN.
YOU MUST NOT FIGHT TSUCHI-GUMO.
>> MASTER!
>> NOT TO WORRY.
THAT’S THE SECRET ART
OF NURARIHYON THAT HE MASTERED
WHILE IN TONO.
HE CANNOT BE SEEN.
KYOKASUIGETSU.
>> I’M NOT SOME AMATEUR!
DON’T INSULT ME!
AAH!
I THINK I’LL START
WITH YOU FIRST! YEAH!
>> RIKUO’S FEAR DIDN’T WORK!
NOT GOOD!
>> YEAH, GOTTA STOP HIM!
>> FALL BACK, RIKUO!
LET US HANDLE THIS YOKAI!
>> HMM.
>> QUIT IT, BASTARD!
>> YOU’RE IN MY WAY!
>> NO, MASTER RIKUO.
>> WHAT’S GOING ON HERE?
WHY ISN’T MY FEAR WORKING?
>> NO!
>> NURA!
>> DON’T, YURA.
YOU WON’T WIN.
>> THEN YOU DO IT!
YOU BEAT HIM THE LAST TIME,
DIDN’T YOU?
>> I DIDN’T BEAT HIM.
I ONLY SEALED HIM.
HE RAN AMOK FOR A MONTH
AFTER ALL THE YOKAI WERE GONE.
>> HUH? A SEAL? SURE.
>> HE WAS BORED AT THAT TIME,
SO I TRICKED HIM INTO
A SLUMBER, THOUGH I DOUBT
HE EXPECTED TO BE SEALED AWAY
FOR 400 YEARS.
HE IS A YOKAI OF GREAT POWER,
ONE WHO HAS LONG WREAKED HAVOC
IN WESTERN JAPAN, A FORCE
THAT’S BEYOND DEFEAT OR CONTROL.
THEY ONCE HAD A SAYING
ABOUT TSUCHI-GUMO.
IF HE IS HUNGRY,
AVOID HIM AT ALL COST.
GODS, BUDDHA, AYAKASHI,
HE WILL DEVOUR THEM ALL.
TRUE MIRACLES ARE RARE THINGS.
I NEVER THOUGHT HE WOULD GO
AFTER THE GRANDSON
WITHOUT ANY WARNING.
>> THAT’S ENOUGH, YOU BASTARD!
>> GET AWAY FROM HIM RIGHT NOW!
>> HUH? JUST HANG ON.
I’LL EAT YOU HUNDRED DEMONS
SOON ENOUGH!
>> HE HASN’T EATEN IN 400 YEARS.
>> ONE BY ONE,
EVERY SINGLE ONE OF YOU.
>> IF TSUCHI-GUMO
IS TRULY HUNGRY...
>> JUST LIKE THIS GUY.
>> HE WILL DEVOUR US ALL.
>> ALL RIGHT, THEN.
WHICH ONE OF YOU
SHOULD I TAKE ON NEXT?
YOU LOOK LIKE A TASTY SNACK.
LET’S START!
>> WE WON’T LET YOU!
>> IS THAT REIRA?
>> DOHIKO!
>> HUH? WHAT THE HELL?
SO YOU’RE A NICE YOKAI, HUH?
MY PIPE’S NOT COMING OUT.
>> YOU BASTARD!
>> DON’T BUTT IN!
YOU SHOULD JUST WAIT
FOR YOUR TURN!
NEXT IS YOU RIGHT THERE!
>> RYUJI, GO AND RETRIEVE
NENEKIRIMARU WHILE YOU CAN.
>> WHY WOULD YOU DO THAT?
>> IN CASE THE WORST HAPPENS.
IS THAT CLEAR, RYUJI?
YOU MUST FLEE.
>> NURA!
>> NEXT WILL BE YOU, THE GIRL.
>> OIKAWA?
FOR OUR MASTER...
>> WHAT THE--
>> MASTER!
THANK GOODNESS
YOU’RE STILL ALIVE.
I THOUGHT HE’D DESTROYED YOU.
I’M RELIEVED, SO RELIEVED,
BECAUSE I CAN’T KEEP
PROTECTING YOU.
>> LOOK AT THIS, HUH?
I CAN’T BELIEVE
THAT YOU’RE STILL ALIVE.
>> YOU’LL HAVE TO DO BETTER
THAN THAT TO KILL ME.
THESE GUYS FOLLOW ME AND
THEY’VE PLEDGED THEIR LOYALTY
TO ME AND MY FEAR.
AS LONG AS I’M ALIVE, I WON’T
LET YOU LAY A HAND ON THEM!
IF YOU WANT TO DESTROY THIS
NIGHT PARADE, THEN YOU’LL HAVE
TO KILL ME FIRST, BASTARD!
>> HE GOT ALL OF YOU?
DAMN IT!
HE’LL PAY FOR THIS!
>> WHAT IS THIS?
>> HE’LL PAY FOR THIS.
HE’S NOT GONNA TOUCH YOU.
>> RIKUO.
>> MY HUNDRED DEMONS!
>> MASTER?
>> HE’S STARTING TO CHANGE BACK?
>> THE SEAL.
THE YOKAI AURA HERE IS FADING.
>> OH, NO!
NURA, YOU CAN’T FIGHT HIM
LIKE THAT!
GET BACK! NURA!
>> AAH!
>> YOKAI BATTLES ARE ALL ABOUT
FEAR, BUT THIS THING
DOESN’T FEAR ANYTHING.
HE CAN DESTROY A NIGHT PARADE
HIMSELF.
>> STOP IT, RIKUO!
>> HUH?
>> MASTER RIKUO!
>> OH, WOW! HE ACTUALLY CUT HIM!
>> HUH?
>> THE NENEKIRIMARU.
NOW WATCH CLOSELY, YOU TWO.
THAT’S NENEKIRIMARU.
>> WHAT THE HELL IS THIS?
>> MASTER RIKUO!
HIS TECHNIQUE STARTED WORKING
ON HIM?
>> I’VE SEEN THIS BEFORE.
HIS TWO FORMS ARE OVERLAPPING.
>> AAH!
>> DON’T GET COCKY!
>> THE COMMANDER IS FACING
A RELENTLESS ONSLAUGHT.
IF HE LOSES, HIS HUNDRED DEMONS
WILL NOT BE ABLE TO CALL FORTH
THEIR POWER NO MATTER HOW
EXCEPTIONAL THEY ARE.
TSUCHI-GUMO’S FEAR...
>> AAH!
>> WILL DESTROY
THEIR NIGHT PARADE.
>> WHAT WAS THAT?
YOU AREN’T JOKING, ARE YOU?
>> NO, SO DON’T WORRY.
I MADE SURE TO SEND SOMEBODY
THAT I HAVE COMPLETE FAITH IN.
>> I GUESS YOU ARE
A DOTING GRANDFATHER.
>> HA! HE WOULDN’T TAKE NO
FOR AN ANSWER.
>> HUH.
I’M DONE.
THIS IS BORING.
I WONDER IF I’LL BE ABLE
TO FIND MORE PREY
TO ENJOY SOMEWHERE ELSE.
>> MASTER?
>> RIKUO?
>> I’M NOT GONNA LOSE.
NOT HERE.
>> WHAT IS THE DEAL WITH YOU?
WHY DON’T YOU JUST DIE?
>> MASTER?
>> PLEASE DON’T STAND UP.
>> NO, I HAVE TO
BECAUSE I’M THE COMMANDER.
>> IT LOOKS LIKE I DIDN’T
DESTROY HIS HUNDRED DEMONS
JUST YET.
INTERESTING.
YOU KNOW, YOU’RE PRETTY GOOD.
I’LL BE ABLE TO KILL
SOME TIME WITH YOU.
>> HEY, GET YOUR HANDS OFF HER!
>> I’LL HANG OUT
AT SOKOKUJI TEMPLE.
BE THERE AND BRING THOSE
HUNDRED DEMONS OF YOURS.
>> WAIT! HOLD ON! COME BACK!
TSUCHI-GUMO!
>> WHERE ARE WE?
>> IS THIS THE PLACE, MY LADY?
>> YES. I WILL BEAR MY CHILD
HERE.
HOW I’VE WAITED
AND AFTER OVER A MILLENNIA.
>> MY LADY?
>> COME BACK! IT’S DANGEROUS!
>> I’LL BE FINE, KYOKOTSU.
>> IT’S SO DARK.
>> KEEP YOUR HANDS OUT OF IT!
>> HUH?
>> IT’S BLACK FOR A REASON.
ALL THE HATRED IN KYOTO
WAS RELEASED WHEN THE SEALS
WERE BROKEN AND IT HAS DYED
THIS LAKE’S WATERS.
AND ALSO, THIS IS WHERE
OUR LADY GAVE BIRTH
FOR THE VERY FIRST TIME.
NUEGAIKE POND, IT’S CALLED.
DARKNESS SURROUNDS IT.
IT’S WHERE NUE WILL BE BORN.
>> LORD ZEN, PLEASE, THIS WAY!
>> OVER HERE! WE NEED YOU HERE!
>> DAMN IT!
I HEARD YOU ALREADY, SO QUIT
CALLING FOR ME ALL AT ONCE!
JUST TAKE ALL THE CRITICALLY
WOUNDED TO THE TREASURE SHIP.
>> THAT WAS WEIRD.
I USUALLY HAVE MORE STRENGTH
THAN THAT.
>> IT WAS LIKE I DIDN’T HAVE
ANY POWER.
>> HOW IS RIKUO?
WITH THAT TERRIBLE BEATING
HE TOOK, IT’S AMAZING
THAT HE’S STILL ALIVE.
WHAT ARE WE GOING TO DO?
MAYBE WE JUMPED INTO THIS
TOO SOON.
>> HUH?
>> HOW CAN YOU CALL YOURSELF
THE LEADER OF THE NURA CLAN
LOOKING LIKE THAT?
HAND OVER YOUR COMMANDER.
I’LL HANDLE THIS.
>> GYUKI!
>> LET’S GO, RIKUO.
>> WHAT’S SHE DOING?
>> NOSTALGIC.
THE GATHERING OF HATRED FILLS
MY WHOLE BODY WITH STRENGTH.
IT’S TELLING ME TO BREAK
THE SEAL AND GIVE BIRTH.
>> OH! OH!
HOLY MOTHER, ARE YOU BEARING
OUR GOD AT LAST?
>> I SWEAR, SHOKERA,
I’M GOING TO KILL YOU.
SHE’S GIVING BIRTH TO NUE AND
IT’S HAGOROMO-GITSUNE, NOT
HOLY MOTHER, YOU RELIGIOUS NUT.
>> MOTHER OF DARKNESS
IS HER TITLE.
>> DON’T GIVE PEOPLE
WEIRD NICKNAMES.
ARE YOU TRYING TO BE FUNNY
HERE, MAGGOT?
>> NO, I’M NOT, IBARAKI-DOJI.
WE’VE ALL LABORED FOR 400 YEARS
TO ACHIEVE THIS, HAVEN’T WE?
>> WILL YOU TWO STOP ARGUING?
>> [ LAUGHS ]
THEY DON’T ALONG, DO THEY?
BUT STILL, THEY DO PUT THEIR
DIFFERENCES ASIDE WHEN THEY’RE
IN FRONT OF OUR LADY.
>> IBARAKI-DOJI, SHOKEREA,
KYOTO IS NOW OUR DEMON CAPITAL.
GO AND GATHER HUMAN LIVERS
FOR ME TO DINE ON, WON’T YOU?
>> OF COURSE.
>> I WILL DISPATCH EVERY ASSET.
WE SHALL COLLECT 10,000 LIVERS
BEFORE THE NIGHT’S END.
>> [ LAUGHS ]
THE NIGHT PARADE
OF A HUNDRED DEMONS, ONE THE
RIGHTFUL LORD OF PANDEMONIUM
DESERVES.
>> SO HE HAS A GRANDCHILD
AS WELL.
I SEE.
HE CONSORTED WITH HUMANS, TOO.
THIS UNPREDICTABLE BLOOD
FRUSTRATES MY PLANS.
NURARIHYON’S GRANDSON,
BUT STILL THE FOX’S CURSE
WILL NEVER FADE.
THE BLOOD LINE WILL SURELY END
NURARIHYON’S CURSED BLOOD.
>> RIKUO, GET AWAY!
>> RUN, RIKUO,
AWAY FROM THE DARKNESS!
>> WHO WAS THAT?
WHO WAS THE ONE
WHO KILLED MY FATHER?
>> WHO WAS THE ONE
WHO MADE MY MOTHER CRY?
WHO?
YOU! TSUCHI-GUMO!
I’LL KEEP NURARIHYON’S BLOOD
ALIVE.
I’LL CUT THROUGH HIS FEAR!
I CAN’T REACH HIM. WHY?
I KEEP DODGING AND SWINGING
MY SWORD HOPING TO HIT HIM,
BUT NOTHING CONNECTS.
BUT WHY DOESN’T IT?
WHY? WHY?
[ GASP ]
GYUKI! WHERE AM I?
WHERE IS EVERYONE?
WHAT HAPPENED TO ME?
>> I BROUGHT YOU HERE.
WHERE ARE YOU GOING?
>> TO BEAT TSUCHI-GUMO!
THERE’S NO TIME!
TSURARA NEEDS SAVING!
>> AS YOU ARE NOW, IT’S USELESS,
SINCE EVEN THE FEAR OF ONE
OF YOUR NIGHT PARADES
CAN OVERWHELM YOU.
>> WHAT’S THAT?
>> THE LEADER OF THE NURA CLAN
MUST NEVER SUFFER A LOSS.
>> GYUKI’S FEAR?
>> YOU BLOCKED IT.
SO NOW WHAT?
>> HUH?
>> IT’S CLEAR THAT WHEN YOU
WENT TO TONO TO TRAIN,
YOU GAINED GREATER INSIGHT
INTO YOURSELF AND INTO THE VERY
ESSENCE OF A NURARIHYON YOKAI,
BUT THAT’S ALL YOU LEARNED.
YOU CAN CUT THROUGH FEAR
AND CATCH OPPONENTS UNAWARE, BUT
THAT’S THE LIMIT OF YOUR SKILL.
>> HUH? THE LIMIT?
>> RIKUO, IT’S TRUE YOU’VE
GOTTEN STRONGER THESE PAST FEW
MONTHS, BUT IN KYOTO,
THAT ISN’T ENOUGH.
[ SINGING IN JAPANESE ]
>> ARE YOU DONE REPENTING?
I SHALL PASS JUDGMENT.
>> BUT HOW?
I’M THREE-QUARTERS HUMAN!
>> ATONE IN HELL, SCUM.
THAT’S RIGHT.
I JUST HAVE TO KILL THEM.