[ PANTING ]
>> RIKUO, IT’S TRUE.
YOU’VE GOTTEN STRONGER
THESE PAST FEW MONTHS,
BUT IN KYOTO,
THAT ISN’T ENOUGH.
FOR YOUR SWORD
TO REACH ITS POTENTIAL,
THERE ARE TWO THINGS
THAT YOU MUST DO:
BECOME STRONGER,
STRONGER THAN YOUR OWN BLOOD.
>> STRONGER THAN MY OWN BLOOD?
WHAT DO YOU MEAN BY THAT?
>> GYUKI!
WORDS WON’T HELP HIM UNDERSTAND.
ONLY ACTUAL COMBAT WILL.
>> WHO’S THAT?
>> YOUR RIGHT.
RIKUO, DRAW YOUR SWORD.
MASTER THE LORD OF
A HUNDRED DEMONS TECHNIQUE.
>> TECHNIQUE?
WHAT ARE YOU TRYING
TO TELL ME, GYUKI?
>> DRAW YOUR SWORD!
>> WHAT?
HE’S COMPLETELY
DIFFERENT FROM BEFORE.
IS THIS THE REAL GYUKI?
>> YOU MUST NOW SURPASS
YOURSELF, RIKUO.
>> MMM.
>> LOOK AT THAT!
[ GASPING ]
>> WHAT’S GOING ON UP THERE?
>> A CASTLE?
>> WHAT THE HECK?
>> THAT’S NIJO CASTLE.
DOES THIS MEAN
THE FINAL SEAL WAS BROKEN?
TIME HAS RUN OUT!
>> ALL RIGHT.
WE SHOULD HEAD TO THE NEXT SEAL.
OUR SITUATION REMAINS THE SAME.
LET US MOVE PAST THAT
UNFORTUNATE ENCOUNTER
WITH TSUCHI-GUMO.
WHERE’S YOUR ENTHUSIASM?
>> ARE YOU JOKING?
>> HOW CAN WE JOIN FORCES
WITH THINGS AS BAD AS THEY ARE?
>> WE DON’T FOLLOW ONMYOJI.
>> AND BESIDES,
MASTER RIKUO ISN’T HERE.
THERE’S NO REASON
FOR US TO FIGHT.
>> THEY’RE SO INDIFFERENT.
WHAT’S WITH THEM?
>> NO.
THAT’S JUST HOW YOKAI ARE.
A NIGHT PARADE NEEDS ITS LEADER
AND IT WOULD SEEM THAT BOY
DID HAVE WHAT IT TAKES
TO BECOME THEIR MASTER.
>> NURA?
>> BUT TIME IS STILL SHORT,
SO WHAT SHALL WE DO NOW?
>> WHAT’S WITH YOU ALL?
COME ON!
>> HEY! KEJORO!
>> MASTER RIKUO WOULD BE
DISAPPOINTED IF HE SAW THIS!
WE ALL HAVE TO KEEP
THIS NIGHT PARADE GOING!
>> ALL RIGHT! ALL RIGHT!
>> LET’S GO, EVERYONE!
SHOW ME THAT YOU’RE LOOKING OUT
FOR MASTER RIKUO’S
HUNDRED DEMONS!
>> THE DEN MOTHER, EH?
>> YOU TONO GUYS, TOO!
>> WE TAKE ORDERS FROM NO ONE.
WE’LL HANDLE THINGS OUR OWN WAY.
[ SIGHS ]
>> WELL, AT LEAST I TRIED.
HEY, KUBINASHI, CAN YOU LEAD US?
KUBINASHI?
>> I LOST.
IN THE END, I COULDN’T
PROTECT WHAT I SAID I WOULD.
WAS THIS ALL I COULD MANAGE?
THE STRINGER OF JOSHU?
HOW LONG AM I GOING TO CLING
TO THAT OLD NICKNAME?
THE SECOND HEIR
PASSED AWAY YEARS AGO.
IT FEELS LIKE I’VE FORGOTTEN
SOMETHING IMPORTANT SINCE THEN.
[ GASPS ]
>> IT’S HUGE AND DIFFERENT
FROM BEFORE!
SO THIS...
THIS IS GYUKI’S FEAR!
HIS TRUE POWER AS A YOKAI!
IS HE TRAINING ME?
>> THAT’S MORE LIKE IT.
NOW TRY TO REPEL MY FEAR
IN THAT HUMAN FORM.
THERE IS ONE THING THAT YOU
MUST DO, HOWEVER, AND THAT IS
TO STRENGTHEN YOUR FEAR!
[ GRUNTS ]
>> LISTEN, RIKUO.
THE STRENGTH OF A NIGHT PARADE
IS PROPORTIONAL
TO ITS SUPREME COMMANDER’S.
THE STRONGER THE LEADER,
THE GREATER THE STRENGTH OF
THE NIGHT PARADE OF
A HUNDRED DEMONS.
CONVERSELY, IF THE COMMANDER’S
FEAR IS WEAK, THEN THE GROUP
IS NO BETTER THAN
A LOWLY BAND OF MISFITS.
[ GRUNTS ]
>> IN OTHER WORDS, COME STRONG
AND YOU CAN BUILD AN INVINCIBLE
NIGHT PARADE OF A HUNDRED DEMONS
AND THE STRENGTH OF
THE NIGHT PARADE
WILL IN TURN BE YOURS.
[ WHIMPERS ]
>> WHEN YOU BECOME
A TRUE WARRIOR
WHO FORGES STRONG BONDS
AND IS TRUSTED BY ALL,
YOU ARE REWARDED
WITH A GREAT POWER.
THAT’S THE NEXT TECHNIQUE THAT
YOU MUST GAIN
POSSESSION OF, RIKUO.
OUR FOE STRENGTHENS
WITH EACH REBIRTH.
THAT’S WHY YOU MUST SURPASS
YOUR GRANDFATHER AS WELL
AS YOUR FATHER.
>> SURPASS THEM?
BUT HOW?
I’M THREE-QUARTERS HUMAN!
HOW CAN I SURPASS MY GRANDPA?
>> DON’T CONSIDER
YOUR HUMANITY A WEAKNESS.
AFTER ALL, THE ERA WHEN
THE NURA CLAN WAS STRONGEST
WAS DURING YOUR FATHER’S REIGN
DESPITE THE HALF-HUMAN BLOOD
IN HIS VEINS.
>> WHAT?
>> YOU ONCE DENIED
THAT PART OF YOU WAS AYAKASHI.
I TOLD YOU ON MT. NEJIREME
TO CAST OFF YOUR HUMAN SIDE.
THAT WAS TO COMPEL YOU
TO FACE YOUR FUTURE AS
A SUPREME COMMANDER
OF AYAKASHI!
[ SHOUTS ]
>> AND WHEN YOU ACKNOWLEDGED
THE PART OF YOU
THAT WAS AYAKASHI,
YOU BECAME STRONGER.
YOU MUST NOW ACCEPT THE PART
OF YOU THAT IS HUMAN, RIKUO.
YOUR FATHER DID.
HE ACKNOWLEDGED THAT HE WAS
BOTH HUMAN AND AYAKASHI.
IT MADE HIM STRONG.
DON’T REJECT YOURSELF.
ACCEPT WHO YOU ARE AND
YOU’LL BECOME STRONGER FOR IT!
>> GYUKI ISN’T YOUR
ONLY OPPONENT!
TRY TO CUT THROUGH
OUR FEAR IN THAT FORM!
[ SHOUTS ]
[ YELLING ]
>> HEY, WHAT IS THAT?
>> I DON’T SEE ANYTHING.
>> BIKERS.
WE SHOULD PROBABLY
GET OUT OF HERE NOW!
>> WHAT? IS SOMETHING GOING ON?
>> THIS MIGHT BE WHY
IT’S SUPPOSED TO BE
DANGEROUS OUT AT NIGHT.
>> GO OUT AND COLLECT
HUMAN LIVERS TO GIVE LADY
HAGOROMO-GITSUNE THE STRENGTH
SHE NEEDS TO BEAR HER CHILD.
>> HELP!
SOMEONE HELP!
>> HEY, BABE!
[ LAUGHS ]
LET’S HAVE SOME FUN!
>> NO! LET ME GO!
>> JUST GIVE ME YOUR LIVER!
>> NO!
[ SHOUTS ]
>> STOP THAT.
>> HUH?
WHO THE HELL ARE YOU?
>> IS THAT WHAT
THE KYOTO YOKAI ARE AFTER?
I’M THE ONE
WHO SHOULD STOP DOING THIS.
YOU REALLY ARE LOW-LIFES.
TRYING TO BE RIGHTEOUS.
I’LL LOSE AGAIN AT THIS RATE.
>> IS THIS GUY A YOKAI?
HIS HEAD FELL RIGHT OFF!
>> HEY, ISN’T HE
IN THE NURA CLAN?
>> YEAH, YOU’RE RIGHT!
THE OTHERS WERE SAYING
STUFF ABOUT YOU GUYS!
>> YEAH, THAT THE NURA CLAN GUYS
ARE A BUNCH OF LOSERS!
[ LAUGHTER ]
>> YOU’D THINK THAT’D BRING
TEARS TO MY EYES,
BUT IT MAKES ME WANT TO LAUGH.
>> WHAT ARE YOU
SMILING FOR, LOSER?
>> HIS HEAD!
>> TAKE THIS! AND THAT!
>> MISTER, I KNOW YOU’RE
A YOKAI, BUT PLEASE GET UP!
YOU’VE GOTTA HELP ME,
SO WAKE UP! WAKE UP!
>> WAKE UP.
THAT SOUNDS SO FAMILIAR.
>> HEY THERE, MR. BAD.
TIME FOR YOU TO WAKE UP.
COME ON NOW.
[ SHOUTS ]
>> WHAT THE HELL?
>> RIGHT.
IT’S SUCH A SIMPLE SOLUTION.
HOW COULD I HAVE FORGOTTEN
ABOUT IT FOR SO LONG?
[ SCREAMS ]
>> THAT’S RIGHT.
I JUST HAVE TO KILL THEM.
[ CRYING ]
>> I’M KUBINASHI.
THE IDEA OF ME PROTECTING
SOMETHING ISN’T NATURAL,
SECOND HEIR.
MY JOB IS TO GO AROUND
KILLING AYAKASHI JUST LIKE
I USED TO BEFORE I MET YOU.
>> KUBINASHI?
DID YOU DO ALL THIS?
>> YOU WAIT HERE.
I’M GOING TO GO PLAY WITH
THE KYOTO YOKAI FOR A BIT.
>> HMM.
>> IT’S NOT ENOUGH.
QUICKLY NOW, BRING THEM TO ME.
MORE LIVERS, QUICKLY.
I REQUIRE FURTHER HUMAN LIVERS.
GIVE ME STRENGTH, MY SERVANTS,
STRENGTH TO GIVE BIRTH TO NUE.
[ CACKLING ]
>> WHAT IS IT?
>> APOLOGIES.
IT’S REGARDING THE EIGHTH SEAL
AND NOW THE SEVENTH ONE, TOO.
>> WHAT’S THAT?
>> HASHIRA VILLA.
>> WHAT HAPPENED?
>> WHAT A MESS.
>> THIS GARDEN IS LIKE
A PICTURE OF HELL NOW.
>> DID SOME MONSTER PASS
THROUGH?
>> I SENSE TREMENDOUS
ANGER HERE.
WHO COULD HAVE REDUCED
POWERFUL AYAKASHI TO THIS?
>> THIS IS KUBINASHI’S WORK.
>> SERIOUSLY?
>> KUBINASHI DID ALL THIS?
>> IS IT POSSIBLE THAT HE
LOST HIMSELF IN HIS ANGER?
>> KURO, ISN’T IT DANGEROUS
LETTING KUBINASHI
GO ON LIKE THIS?
>> YOU’RE RIGHT.
LET’S GO.
>> IT SEEMS THEY HAVE
A FEW JUGGERNAUTS.
THEY MUST HAVE JOINED
THE NURA CLAN AFTER I DIED.
BUT WHY WOULD SUCH AYAKASHI
FOLLOW ONE SO YOUNG
OUT OF OBLIGATION?
THE NURA CLAN, THEY STIR MY
CURIOSITY EVEN AFTER 400 YEARS.
>> RYUENJI TEMPLE.
>> WHAT IS THIS PLACE?
>> I HAVE NO IDEA.
>> WHY DO YOU SCHEDULE THIS
LAST-MINUTE TRIP TO A TEMPLE
SO LATE AT NIGHT?
>> FOR A TEST?
>> WELCOME, CHILDREN.
I’M GLAD YOU CAME.
>> WHAT’S GOING ON?
>> I DIDN’T KNOW THAT
YOU HAD A TWIN BROTHER, SIR.
[ GROWLING ]
>> SIR?
>> WHAT’S GOING ON?
[ GROWLING ]
>> WHAT ARE THESE THINGS?
[ SCREAMS ]
>> HUMAN LIVERS!
HUMAN LIVERS!
>> YOU’RE THE ONES
GUARDING THE SEAL.
[ SCREAMING ]
>> THESE GUYS WERE JOKES.
>> DEATH TENDRILS, SNAKE BLADE.
IT’S LIKE HOW WE WAS
BEFORE MEETING THE SECOND HEIR.
YOU FOOL!
AT THIS RATE, YOU’LL SLIP
BACK TO YOUR OLD SELF!
>> KEJORO, LET’S GO.
>> I CAN’T LET HIM.
KUBINASHI!
OH!
>> I SMELL BLOOD LIKE
THE STINK OF AN IRON BLADE
DRIPPING WITH FRESH BLOOD.
I SMELL IT COMING FROM YOU.
WHAT’S YOUR NAME, BASTARD?
>> SORRY, I’M STILL IN THE
MIDDLE OF RECLAIMING IT.
>> YOU DRUNK OR SOMETHING?
I WAS SENT HERE TO TAKE CARE
OF THINGS AT THIS SEAL.
HAGOROMO-GITSUNE SAID THERE
WAS A NICE GARDEN HERE,
A DRY LANDSCAPED ONE.
BUT I WAS GREETED BY
THE SMELL OF BLOOD
AND MY GUYS SCATTERED
AROUND LIKE BLOODY PEBBLES.
SO WHAT’S MY POINT HERE?
IT’S THAT YOU’VE SMEARED MUD ON
MY FACE, ON ME, IBARAKI-DOJI.
I’VE GOT NOTHING TO SAY.
I’LL JUST KILL YOU RIGHT NOW.
ATONE IN HELL, SCUM!
>> IS THAT NIJO CASTLE UP THERE?
IT’S AN ENORMOUS STRUCTURE
THAT APPEARED OUT OF NOWHERE.
AND WITH THIS BIZARRE PHENOMENON
ALONG WITH THE MISSING PEOPLE,
THERE ARE MANY
UNANSWERED QUESTIONS.
>> YAMADA?
YAMADA?
>> WHAT ARE YOU?
>> THEY’RE MONSTERS!
[ SCREAMING ]
>> WHAT HAPPENED?
WHAT’S GOING ON IN KYOTO?
>> WASN’T THAT TV STATION
SOMEWHERE NEAR NIJO CASTLE?
>> WE’RE CLOSE, TOO.
>> I CAN’T BELIEVE THIS
IS HAPPENING!
>> WHY DID WE HAVE
TO COME TO KYOTO!
>> NOW JUST HOLD ON A MINUTE,
YOU TWO!
WE’VE NEVER BEEN SO CLOSE
TO ACTUALLY PROVING
THAT YOKAI EXIST!
HUNTING FOR YOKAI
ALWAYS INVOLVES SOME RISK.
IT’S THE ULTIMATE TEST OF
THE KIYOJUJI PARANORMAL PATROL!
>> I DON’T WANT TO HEAR
THAT CRAP!
WHY DON’T YOU JUST
GO ON YOUR OWN?
>> THERE’S NOTHING MORE
I’D RATHER DO, BUT...
I BEG YOU!
EVEN JUST A PICTURE
OF NIJO CASTLE WOULD BE FINE!
>> YOU CAN’T LEAVE!
>> WOULD YOU CUT
THAT OUT ALREADY?
>> THIS ISN’T THE RIGHT
TIME FOR THIS!
>> I WANNA GO HOME!
>> THERE’S NOTHING
TO WORRY ABOUT.
>> HUH?
>> JUST RELAX, OKAY?
>> KURATA?
[ SHOUTING ]
[ COUGHING ]
>> THEY BROKE THROUGH!
>> DAMN! THE SEAL FAILED!
>> LADY HAGOROMO-GITSUNE DESIRES
HUMAN LIVERS, ESPECIALLY
FROM GIFTED PEOPLE
SUCH AS YOURSELVES.
YOUR FLESH SHALL BE
AN OFFERING TO OUR GOD.
HOW I ENVY ALL OF YOU.
[ GRUNTING ]
>> IT’S A CURSE
THAT MINE IS UNFIT.
I WOULD GLADLY TAKE YOUR PLACE.
DEATH IS AT HAND.
LORD, SHINE DOWN
YOUR BENEVOLENT LIGHT!
>> YOU BASTARD!
>> YOU’VE MADE IT QUITE FAR,
KYOTO YOKAI.
I PRESUME THAT YOU ARE ALL
PREPARED FOR THE CONSEQUENCES
OF DOING SO.
>> 27th HEIR!
>> TAKE YOUR POSITIONS!
MAKE THIS YOKAI REGRET
INVADING OUR SACRED ESTATE!
KEIKAIN ONMYO JUTSU,
CHAIN OF SPELLS!
>> YOU WON’T GET OUT ALIVE!
NOT AFTER BREAKING IN!
>> ARE YOU DONE REPENTING?
>> GET BACK IN YOUR POSITIONS!
>> AND NOW I SHALL
PASS JUDGMENT.
>> WHAT’S WITH THAT STRING?
INVOKE DEVIL’S DRUM!
THAT WON’T HELP.
[ GRUNTS ]
>> MY THUNDER ARROWS WORK WELL,
DON’T THEY?
YOU’RE STILL ALIVE?
YOU’D BE BETTER OFF DEAD.
YOU WOULDN’T HAVE
TO SUFFER THEN.
>> YOUR THUNDER ARROWS
NEED SOME WORK.
THEY DIDN’T HURT.
>> ENOUGH! HUH?
A DOUBLE MADE OF STRING?
>> GOTCHA.
>> SORRY.
MY DEVIL’S DRUM CAN FIRE
IN ANY DIRECTION.
>> THIS YOKAI AURA, COULD
IT BE THAT YOKAI FROM BEFORE?
>> IT WOULD SEEM
THAT YOU’RE STILL ALIVE.
[ GROWLS ]
>> YOU’LL PAY FOR THIS!
>> DRIED ACONITE ROOT.
>> NEVER OPEN THIS POT.
IT CONTAINS DRIED ACONITE ROOT,
A POISON.
>> STOP IT, RYUJI.
IT’S A POISON.
>> WHAT ARE YOU TALKING ABOUT?
HE’S LYING.
WHEN HE SAYS THAT STUFF,
HE’S USUALLY HIDING CANDY
OR SOMETHING.
LEARN ALL THE FAMILY HEADS’
WEAKNESSES. IT’S HANDY.
SO ARE YOU IN OR NOT?
>> THERE’S NO ARGUING WITH HIM.
>> BIRDIES.
>> IT’S DARK.
TRY IT, AKIFUSA.
>> WHAT?
>> IT’S SOY SAUCE.
>> WHAT’S HE HIDING
SOY SAUCE FOR?
THAT’S BORING.
>> LET’S GO!
>> HOLD ON, RYUJI!
>> MIX, MIX, MIX.
>> WHAT ARE YOU DOING HERE?
I SPECIAL ORDERED THAT!
IT’S TOP TAMARI MADE
FROM NATURAL FERMENTED
OTSUKA SOY SAUCE!
>> GRANDPA, THIS IS REALLY
GREAT ON TKG.
>> YURA, YOU LIKE TKG TOO?
>> THUS, A STRANGE BOND WAS
FORMED AROUND TAMAGO KAKE GOHAN.
>> THOSE TWO SURE GET ALONG.
>> OH, HOW’D SHE DO IT?
>> THE END.
>> ALL RIGHT,
COME AND GET US, YOU DEMONS!
>> EVERY HUMAN IS
AN OFFERING TO OUR GOD.
>> STAND YOUR GROUND.
THIS PLACE CAN’T FALL!
>> THE BIRTH OF NUE.