[ALICE] Nice work, Ryo!
You followed my orders,
therefore you were able to win.
Yeah, that I did.
Well, that's one victory
under our belt.
Let Central have a taste of
what defeat is like!
[AZAMI]
That was quite the spectacle.
[STUDENT 1]
Whoa, isn't that, Azami Nakiri?
[STUDENT 2] Seriously?!
[ALICE]
Uncle Azami, long time, no see.
Ms. Alice, what have you been
spending so much time writing?
[ALICE] Letters! I'm sending
them airmail to Japan.
Erina was really insistent
that I send them to her.
She's so helpless that
I'm sending her a whole
bunch of them.
Although I find it
really quite a pain. [giggle]
Oh, that so?
[RYO] You look excited to me.
Goodbye, Erina.
Um, Alice...
Please be sure to always
write me, okay?
[giggle]
[ALICE] Huh? I still
haven't gotten anything?
Nothing from Erina? Aww...
Well, thanks, Mom.
I'll just write her
some more then!
Jeez, Erina was the one who
insisted I send them to her
in the first place.
[AZAMI] Hello, Alice.
I appreciate you
looking out for Erina.
Oh, is that so?
[music playing]
[ERINA] The Chief of the
Cutting Edge Club?
So when did Alice
gain that position?
Look, it's listed right
here in the official
records of past Food Wars.
It's why she was a target of
the straggler-hunters.
Alice... I hope she's okay.
Oh, you're worried about her,
huh?
I...
I'm not concerned about her!
It's just that she has a habit
of being kinda reckless.
Well, she is the one who went
to the trouble of breaking you
out of the mansion.
Heh, I get the impression
that Alice is as equally
worried about you.
You two have a
beautiful friendship.
Ah, what youth!
I do wonder about that though.
Huh?
I find it hard to believe
that she would even care,
not when it comes to me anyway.
After all, I've done many
terrible things to her
over the years.
[AZAMI] Alice, your Cutting Edge
Club is the only one who won
in today's straggler hunt.
The other 32 groups have
all lost their rounds.
They will be
officially disbanded.
Regardless of the other groups,
Ryo was declared
the victor against Central.
Can you still stand there and
tell us that your plan's
the right thing to do?
That it is the only way?
I'm disappointed, Alice.
I thought better of you.
I thought you of all people
would support my plan
in creating one "true cuisine".
Those of the Nakiri family
have a duty
to lead the world of gourmet
food to new horizons.
And my sweeping reforms
shall accomplish that.
It's my father!
Alice...
I can't simply accept your
methods in good conscience.
Nor should I.
And that's final.
Oh, my dear...
You're quite the naughty girl.
Considering you kidnapped
my beloved daughter
right out from under me,
I don't think you have any
grounds to try and talk.
That's neither here
nor there, Uncle.
Right now, I'm just upset.
I will never forget
your transgressions.
Uncle Azami, these last few
years have taught me something.
I hate you!
I'll no longer allow someone
like you, to ever...
influence Totsuki, nor Erina!
[ERINA] (samll gasp)
[AZAMI] Is that so?
Well, you are welcome to try.
But as for today,
I'll congratulate you
on your one and only victory.
[gasp] Erina...
Did you hear all that?
[AZAMI] (irritated breath)
[ALICE] If Uncle Azami hadn't
gotten in the way, just think.
For all of those lost years,
the two of us could have been
so much closer with each other.
Now, if you'll excuse me.
Um...
[ALICE] But first...
You need to fix that
gloomy look on your face!
And you should focus on being
more dignified, Erina!
You've been spending all
your time moping in the
Kyokusei Dorm!
[ERINA] What is with this
attitude of yours?!
You're the one who took me
from my home, Alice!
[ALICE] Because, I couldn't
stand watching you whimper
in fear of Uncle Azami!
[ERINA] (gasp)
[ALICE] You have to show that
evil man what you're made of!
Let that jerk know who you are,
and that you're not going to
let him push you around!
You can't go hide in your shell
all the time! You hear me?
Alice...
[ALICE] Listen,
I need you in top form,
because someday I plan to
crush you in utter defeat!
And if I plan to use you
as a big stepping stone,
it won't look good if you're
moping around like a hot mess!
[Grrr...] As if you even could!
[ALICE] What did you say?
[ERINA] Your cooking is
nothing but rancid rubbish!
[ALICE]
Did you just insult my food?!
[ERINA]
I did, because it's terrible!
[argument continues]
I gather they must be
really good friends then.
Yeah, but don't ever say that,
or else there'll be big trouble.
[AZAMI] The groups that
have lost shall be
immediately disbanded,
and no further
activities allowed.
If any rebellious plots
are uncovered,
those involved shall be
purged from the school.
Have a nice day.
[SOMA] The content of our
classes have totally changed,
at least, ever since Central
was established.
Yeah... The classes where we
made original dishes are gone,
and now all we do is follow
all of Central's recipes
to the letter.
Seems they've no intention of
letting us cook how we want.
SOMA Even working in
Chef Kojiro's kitchen came
with more freedom than this.
[KOJIRO] (shudder)
[pot clatters]
What's the matter? You okay?
For some reason I just got
REALLY annoyed.
[sliding door opens]
[MAN] The teacher who was
in charge of this class
has been dismissed,
after refusing to follow any
of Central's new policies.
[STUDENTS] (shocked chatter)
So then, they're not
pulling any punches.
[MEGUMI] (shocked squeal)
As such, a substitute teacher
will be coming to perform
today's lesson.
Today will serve as an example
of the "true cuisine" that
Central is advocating.
Please make sure you
learn the recipe.
Now then,
I'll bring in the substitute.
[SOMA] (gasp)
[STUDENTS] (shocked chatter)
[STUDENT] The first seat...
It's Eishi Tsukasa!
[scared squeal]
[TSUKASA] Hello everyone.
I'm Eishi Tsukasa, first seat
of the Council of Ten.
I'm not certain if any of you
have heard of me before.
[STUDENTS]
(disbelieving) We have!
Today I will be creating
a number of dishes.
When you make them from now on,
we expect that you will follow
my example down to the letter.
Is he serious?!
[GIRL] He's going to
teach us personally?!
[GUY] Oh man, I'm nervous!
[SOMA] We tasted his stuff
at the Lunar Feast,
it was high level.
He was amazing.
Everything we had at his place
was just sublime.
So, um,
for today's recipe then,
I will need one student,
someone to act as my assistant.
I need someone to
support me up here.
Is there anybody who
would like to volunteer?
[shocked and scared]
[GUY] Uh, not me!
[GUY 2] Nope, I can't.
[GIRL] Why don't you go?
[GIRL 2] Are you crazy!
[GUY 3] Not a chance in Hell.
Uh... anyone?
Is having to cook with me
that unpleasant?
Huh?
Soma?!
[STUDENTS] (shocked)
Soma Yukihira...
I wasn't aware you were
even in this class.
Yeah! If it's okay, I'll do it.
Sure. Then you've got the job,
my friend.
You'll be learning 5 different
French "amuse" dishes today.
We'll be cooking them
all at the same time.
Soma, I'll have you handle all
the necessary preparation.
Cool!
[TSUKASA] All right,
let's get cooking.
Soma, first put some semi-dry
figs into a food processor
and ready for a quenelle.
Then cut the shallots haché
and julienne the carrots.
Mix the egg yolks, sugar,
cardamom powder and milk,
then warm them up anglaise.
When it's cool enough,
drizzle it into the sorbetière.
[SOMA] Gotcha!
[STUDENTS] (freaking out)
[GUY] What'd he say?!
[GIRL] My head's gonna explode!
Wow! Look at 'em go!
[TSUKASA] Then, next you'll...
[SOMA] ...coat the sweetfish
in whole wheat flour and
friture them, right?
Oh! Right, please do.
[STUDENTS] (impressed
[SOMA  Chef! The courgette mix
is dressed and ready!
The whipped cream with firm
peaks will be done for you
in about 10 more seconds.
Great.
[SOMA] Almond cuit.
[TSUKASA] Great.
[SOMA] I've had the basics of
French cooking drilled into me
until I was sick of it!
Back at Chef Kojiro's
during my Stagiaire.
Don't get sloppy, Soma.
[SOMA  Right!
All ready for arrangement.
[TSUKASA] Great.
[awestruck] Amazing!
[GIRL] So fast...
[GUY]
These two are on another level.
[MEGUMI] A space where only
the strong may enter...
...a collaboration between
serious chefs!
Now Soma,
give me asparagus grille.
Yes, Chef!
[STUDENTS] (awestruck)
Took 'em no time at all.
It's now time for everyone else
to head to their stations
and get cooking.
Should take you about the
same amount of time.
[STUDENTS] No freakin' way!
Isn't she simply stunning?
[GIRL 2] Come to think of it,
we haven't seen her
in class lately.
That's great. I'm glad to see
Ms Erina is doing so well.
[ERINA] I'm glad I decided
to brush everything aside
and go to class.
It doesn't seem like
Father intends to
force me back, anyway.
Hey, Ms Erina,
that was excellent work today.
Your dish got an A,
as per usual.
It was a cinch, actually.
Your skills are always so
impeccable to witness,
Ms Nakiri.
[ERINA] The Academy's lecturers?
Your father must be so proud
to have you as a daughter.
For the sake of Totsuki Academy
and Central,
we expect terrific things
from you as a chef.
[ERINA] Excuse me.
[MEGUMI] Nice job today, Soma!
[SOMA] Thanks!
You did pretty well yourself.
You were wonderful!
You handled all of that
without batting an eye!
[SOMA] To be honest..
it wasn't nearly as easy
as it may have looked.
Central's level is
a lot higher than- [urk!]
Wait a minute! This means
I totally just helped
Central out, didn't I?!
What the hell was I thinking?!
[arghh!]
[cell phone buzzes]
The Regional Cuisine club is
doing a Food War against
the straggler-hunters!
No way!
I have to go call the Chief now!
Uh...
[TSUKASA] (groans)
What are you still doing here,
Chef Tsukasa?!
Well, once the class finished,
all the nervousness I was
holding back decided
to overwhelm me.
I seriously can't
handle this at all,
cooking in front of the eyes
of so many students.
Just the thought that I might
forget to tell them something
makes me absolutely sick.
I bet Rindo would blow her top
if she saw me acting so weak
and pathetic like this.
Hmm, this dude seems to suffer
from extreme perfectionism.
[TSUKASA]
But I have to say, your
cooking was excellent today.
You are far better than
I gave you credit for.
Same here, man,
I had a pretty good time
and learned quite
a bit from you.
I think you'll prove
quite useful.
[SOMA] (hmm?)
Do you have any interest in
being my right-hand man?
Would you like to join us,
in Central?
[HISAKO] Ms Erina, I heard the
next straggler hunt was decided.
In about three days.
[ERINA] I see.
[HISAKO] Another large number
of groups will be disbanded,
I imagine.
We can't think like that.
It's very possible some of
the groups may win,
like Alice's did the other day.
My Father, as well as
those in Central
are not as invincible as
they may appear to be.
Um? What are you staring at?
Oh, nothing.
I just thought that the
expression on your face
was somehow different
than usual.
And that maybe you were having
a change of heart about things.
Maybe so.
[ERINA] Up until now,
I've listened to my father
without ever holding any
doubts about him.
I never even considered
another possible path.
Because obeying him seemed
perfectly natural to me.
But now, I've seen Soma Yukihira
and the members of the
Kyokusei Dorm
stand up against him without
even yielding an inch.
And even Alice spoke up
right to his face,
and let her anger
be known to him.
Having seen all of that, I...
You have to show that evil man
what you're made of!
Let that jerk know who you are.
I started to think
more seriously.
About what I really want.
What I want to accomplish
as a person.
Wow, Ms Erina...
But... But don't get me wrong,
I mean I wasn't influenced
by Alice or Soma in particular!
I was simply acting of
my own free will.
[huh?] Soma?
I'm telling you that he didn't
have anything to do with my-
Is that Tsukasa with Soma?
Why are those two together?!
What seems to be the matter,
Ms Erina?
Why are we hiding from them?
Well, um, I'm not really sure...
[SOMA] Am I getting this right?
You want me to be
part of Central?
[TSUKASA] That's right.
You're not very good at making
jokes, Chef Tsukasa.
Why would I ever do that?
I see.
I knew you wouldn't agree to it.
Whoa! You don't have to be
THAT depressed about it!
To be perfectly honest,
I'm just pleased as punch
that you've acknowledged
my cooking skills.
have no intention of ever
letting Central get ahold
of the Yukihira family
style of cooking.
[TSUKASA]
Oh, well we don't need that.
What?
We don't want the
Yukihira style.
I simply wanted your abilities.
I think you would make me
excellent support chef.
I think that my cooking
stands to get even better
if you were by my side
assisting me the whole time.
So, um,
that's the gist of it anyway.
Will you at least give it
some honest consideration, Soma?
Perhaps for the sake?
[sigh]
You're being awfully nonchalant
about such a selfishly
blatant request.
You know,
I've never met a single chef
that wasn't in some way
obsessed with themselves.
Hey, Erina and Hisako,
whatcha doing here?
[HISAKO] Hurry and get down!
[MEGUMI] Huh?!
You stand to gain a lot
from this too.
If you join Central
and pair up with me,
you'll be able to cook
on a much higher level
than you do right now.
But I would still be stuck as
being nothing more than your
assistant, isn't that right?
There's no point in me
doing that unless I can
serve up my own food.
[depressed sigh] Okay...
You really have no capacity
for thought outside of yourself,
do you?
Anyway, you've never even seen a
single one of my dishes before,
much less tasted one!
Isn't it possible that my skills
might actually surpass yours
in every conceivable way?
[TSUKASA] Interesting.
Then shall we go ahead
and test that out?
[TSUKASA] Which of us
really belongs at the top?
If you're up for it,
I'll throw down with you
right here and now.
And even put my spot at the
top of the Council of Ten
on the line.
Are you serious?
Definitely.
But if I end up winning
this challenge,
you will join with Central
and serve under me, understand?
Do you accept my challenge?
Soma Yukihira?
[slow exhale]
It would be my pleasure.
Let's do this thing.
This is a battle for
the First Seat!
[hmpf]
Well, then that decides it.
So, about the theme ingredient,
how about venison?
Apparently, it was originally
going to be used in
today's class,
so numerous cuts have
already been prepared.
I see, then.
Works for me.
And as for the cooking style,
let's make it-
We shall make it French.
Oh, yeah? Fine.
Then let's get cooking,
shall we?
The battle begins.
[SOMA] The French cooking that
Chef Tsukasa made for us
during the Lunar Festival...
It really was
out of this world.
But I learned my own tricks
while studying with
Chef Kojiro!
I'll mow him down with
my own French style!
Uh, how do you suppose
it turned into this?
Who knows!
Anything can set these two off.
But now that it's come
to a cook-off,
we MUST see it to the end.
We MUST see how Soma
faces off against Tsukasa.
You're right, Ms Erina.
But then,
if he loses the battle...
Now then, about that venison...
What should I make?
What dish can beat
Eishi Tsukasa?
[TSUKASA] Soma.
I'm going to get started.
[SOMA] (doh!) That's a huge cut!
It must be back meat!
He's using a salamander to
slowly and gently cook the meat
he's infused with
salt and pepper.
[MEGUMI] He lined the bottom of
that frying pan with cubed cuts
of fat and muscle,
so that the meat isn't directly
touching the frying pan itself.
[SOMA] He's taking it off the
heat periodically to arroser,
using the melted fat to
cover the top so that
it doesn't dry out.
His attention to detail
is nearly flawless.
It's as if he's quietly
whispering to each ingredient
with a caress of tender love.
That is exactly what earned him
a seat at the top.
Right now, he is truly
"speaking" directly to
the ingredients.
[TSUKASA] Come on, come on.
This way, darling.
Just a little closer.
That's right, nice and easy.
Now...
If you would please...
find your way onto my plate.
[MEGUMI] Oh, wow!
The juices from the meat are
quietly swelling inside
as if it were
actually a live deer!
Right before us, his ingredients
are slowly working their way
in to a state of
absolute perfection!
[MEGUMI] (whimpering) We aren't
even eating it, and yet...
[HISAKO] Just the look
and smell are enough to...
[BOTH] ...send us flying!
It's all so simply
overwhelming!
[moaning]
His level of skill
and sensibility
have far surpassed those
of any normal human.
Eishi Tsukasa,
the White Knight of the Table.
He has found his way into
the realm of gods who
create supreme cuisine!
[TSUKASA] Don't you need
to start cooking, Soma?
As a member of Central, I can't
afford to lose to the likes
of a rebel first year.
So I've no intention of
going easy on you.
Hey, Chef Tsukasa,
what exactly does Central want
to accomplish here anyway?
Uh...
You should focus on your dish.
Is the goal really just to get
control over the academy
and how it teaches?
I mean, you're already an
incredible chef placed at
a very high caliber.
Even without Central,
you would be massively
successful in my opinion.
No, no, you're giving me way too
much credit, Soma.
But you're right
about one thing.
Central's true goal has
yet to be realized.
And that is to obliterate all of
Japan's restaurants, pronto.
[SOMA] What?!
[TSUKASA]
Oh, don't misunderstand me.
Any restaurant that serve
legitimate cuisine
will be left untouched.
Director Azami put it like this:
We must eliminate any restaurant
that serves horrid sludge,
which cannot be
considered "food".
It is an absolute necessity
if we wish for Japan's cuisine
to truly reach the next level.
For that to happen, we must
gather all the skilled chefs.
In other words, we need to
begin training our soldiers.
The purge going through the
academy right now,
as well as the new classes,
are all intended to enable us
to rid Japan of
inferior restaurants.
"Inferior restaurants"?
That's right. By weeding out all
of the plebeian eateries
that plague the area...
It means that only those which
offer true gourmet cuisine
will be left standing.
That is the future which
Central is striving for.
All the plebeian eateries
in town, huh?
And by that do you mean places
like "Mitamura Western Cuisine"?
Or better yet, my own family's
"Yukihira Japanese Eatery"?
That's right, that is
exactly what we mean.
You would do that, even if it
meant maybe tearing away
a place that someone holds
close to their heart?
I would, absolutely.
I think that would
be unavoidable.
[SOMA] I see... Then obviously,
I can say with certainty
that I'm not suited to be
your right-hand-man.
I will never join
the likes of Central.
I will be the one who will
win this battle today.
[music playing]