[THUG] Get outta there!
[screams and battle sounds]
[ZENJI] We need more people
over by the dining hall- [ack!]
We gotta hold these
fart-knockers off
till Soma win his Food War
and gets our dorm back, dude!
[breaking glass]
They've just broken through
the barricade!
[AOKI] Oh dude! If they get in,
then we're totally toast!
Wait hold on!
Something's strange...
[AOKI]
Yeah, they ain't coming in.
[ZENJI] (vexed sigh)
This is a terrible time
to break my glasses.
(surprised yell)
[YUKI] What is it, Zenji?
It... Check it out!
[YUME] Soma Yukihira has beaten
Etsuya Eizan in their Food War
by three to zero.
Soma Yukihira is the winner!
What the... Soma won?
[YUME] I repeat,
Soma Yukihira is the winner...
[YUKI] What?! But how?
He did it!
[RINDO]
So he friggin' beat the
No. 9 Seat on the Ten...
Still, if his position was
really on the line,
Eizan probably would have
taken it a lot more seriously.
Soma Yukihira...
[RINDO] Hey, Isshiki!
You've been buried in paperwork
for a while now, huh?
But do you realize
what's happening?
Your dorm is about to be knocked
down by Eizan any second now.
It's not the time to be holed up
here ignoring things.
The dorm isn't in trouble of
being knocked down.
[RINDO] [hmm?]
[SATOSHI]
Because Soma has always known
that the true worth of a chef
lies in what's put on the plate
in front of you.
I'm not worried about our dorm
in the least.
I have faith that Soma will
make short work of that
charlatan Eizan.
But what's most important
is what comes after.
That is when the
true fight will begin.
And no matter what
happens today,
we have to prepare for it.
[RINDO] Dammit, once again,
it looks like
things turned out exactly the
way Isshiki thought they would.
[RYOKO] So, we're not getting
kicked out after all!
[YUKI] Whoohoo!
[AOKI]
Whoa! They're all leaving!
[SATO]
Serves you right, A-holes!
[ZENJI]
Kyokusei isn't going anywhere!
Hey, I'm back!
You big ol' dummy!
[SOMA] What the?!
How could you just ghost and
do a Food War like that?!
You shoulda come and
talked to us first!
You truly are irresponsible!
That was nothing short of
stupid, foolish, and moronic!
We were all worried about you,
you know that?
But thank goodness!
I mean it!
Thank you, Soma,
for saving Kyokusei! [sobbing]
Ah, well...
[MEGUMI] Soma...
We're happy you're back home!
Me too!
But, dude, how the heck did you
beat Eizan in a Food War?!
[SOMA]
Well, you know how it goes...
[SATO] I still can't
believe you did it!
[SOMA]
What's with those helmets?
[MEGUMI] Um, well,
they're remnants from
the "Golden Age."
[RYOKO]
We can go into details later,
but let's just
get inside, first.
[YUKI] Yeah! And we can
celebrate Kyokusei Dorm
being saved!
[ZENJI] (gah!) Not in my room!
[music playing]
[cheers and whoops]
[HISAKO]
You did really great, Soma.
Thank you, and you too!
Hey, Soma, I watched your
Food War with Chef Eizan!
It's the Aldini brothers.
Takumi always seems to be in
"lecture mode," doesn't he?
Gripe, gripe, gripe, gripe,
gripe, gripe, gripe!
Wait, he's not getting mad.
He's not going to complain?
I knew it had to be done.
They were threatening
to take away
the very place where
you guys live.
I probably would have done
the same thing.
I bet you would have!
Nice to see you here, Erina!
Oh! I guess you really have been
here at Kyokusei Dorm.
Uh, hi, I hope this means
you're both doing well today.
All right, all right, let's do
this celebration up guys!
You all grab some food
and eat up! [laughs]
He just finished an important
battle, and look at him.
It's like he doesn't have a care
in the world right now.
Yo, Soma,
you are one dope-ass dude!
You totally slayed the
No. 9 Seat in a Food War!
Then does that mean he could
beat that knockers babe, too,
the No. 10 Seat of the council?
Do not insult me,
you Neanderthal!
And who are you calling
"knockers babe"?
Well, you let Yuki call you
"Erina-poo," so...
That crosses the line! You are
showing no respect for me!
Yeah, that's right!
What's more, Ms Erina has shown
dignity in taking the
No. 10 Seat. Her actual skills-
Still, it was me who decided
on the theme for what
we'd be cooking today.
Chef Eizan just came up
with something on the fly,
but it still somehow managed
to be refined.
Before long, I want to battle
under those same conditions.
He's still not satisfied, huh?
Humph!
I totally understand, Soma.
[SOMA] By the way guys,
what happened to the other
seminars and research societies
that looked like
they were done for?
They're in about as much danger
as they were before.
But thanks to you, Soma,
things have somewhat
changed for the better.
Is that our Isshiki
coming home?!
Where have you been
this whole time?!
I'm so sorry, you guys.
But I AM a member of the Ten,
in name at least.
And I was terribly afraid that
if I wasn't careful enough,
Azami would have found a way
to bring down the hammer on us
more than he already has.
You know what? I thought
Isshiki had actually sold us
out to Central.
Yeah, it looked like you
were gonna screw us.
Whah?! No, of course I wouldn't
do that to you guys!
Do you all not get just how much
I love this dorm?!
Kyokusei holds everything
that I care about.
I guess so.
[TAKUMI] Well, regardless,
what did you mean by things
have changed "for the better"?
Well, thanks to today's horrific
Food War embarrassment,
the Azami Administration
has now heard a new voice.
From now on, Central will
accept Food Wars from
societies and seminars
that are facing dissolution.
And of course,
the elected judges
were chosen on the premise
of being impartial!
We still can't change the fact
that the academy is under
Central's control,
but Eizan's cheating ways are
no longer a factor in it.
And it's because of you!
You've brought back
the Food Wars!
Thank you, Soma,
for saving our dorm today.
Nah, no need to thank me.
You should know this place is
really important to me too.
Everyone, let's all be grateful
that Kyokusei has been spared!
Well, that's enough dwelling
on the bad stuff.
Tonight...
we're letting it all hang out!
[ALL] Yeah!
Wait! WHAAT?!
He's got nothing on under there!
Is this guy naked?!
Ohmygod! How unsanitary!
Wha?! You mustn't look at
such things Ms Erina! [sobs]
[laughing]
Well, I see the guy's still got
it, doesn't he?
Sure enough, that right there
is what makes Kyokusei Dorm
what it is.
Know what I mean?
What on Earth is going on
with all of the freaks
that live in this dorm?
How can they just accept him
going around naked with
an apron?!
This dorm is mysterious
to say the least.
Honestly!
It goes beyond "mysterious!"
It's just Gross! And Unsanitary!
Is everything all right?
Hisako, do you maybe know how
to use a washing machine?
Um, a washing machine?
Yeah, I suppose so...
Really? Wow!
Being able to use something
with all those buttons is
pretty amazing.
Um, Ms Erina?
Uh- Look, never mind the
washing machine!
The point is,
in this mysterious dorm,
I've learned so many
things that, up till now,
I didn't know existed,
much less how to do!
O-okay.
[ERINA]
These people really are bizarre.
And at the center of
them all is...
Soma Yukihira.
[ERINA] When Kyokusei Dorm
came under attack
the others thought, well...
that somehow,
Soma would come through
and pull off some sort of
miracle or something.
They trusted him.
And, well...
you thought so too, Hisako.
Huh? You think I did too?
You looked as if you knew
that Soma would somehow
come through in the end.
Why did you have that look
on your face?
Um, I guess it's just...
How can I put this?
I had nothing to base it on,
but...
I just had a feeling about it,
you know?
If anyone can save Totsuki from
the hand of Master Azami...
HE would be the one capable of
pulling it all off, right?
[SATOSHI] Erina! Hisako!
You ladies come join us!
[urk!] [waah!]
Please put some clothes on!
[SATOSHI] What? Clothes?
Clothes are so blech.
[HISAKO] I don't even know
what that means!
[SATOSHI] Wiggle, jiggle...
[HISAKO] (waaahhh!)
[AZAMI] Satoshi Isshiki,
No. 7 Seat on the Ten...
Effective today,
I would have these men
relinquish their positions:
The No. 3 Seat,
Tosuke Megishima,
and the No. 8 Seat,
Terunori Kuga.
Well, that's unexpectedly
quick of you.
And you seem unexpectedly
unmoved by it.
I was fully aware that this was
going to happen to them.
Any members of the Ten
who do not agree with
Central's wishes
are acting as an obstacle
in our way, are they not?
Your quick thinking is a boon.
The other members of the Ten
are in agreement.
Seriously?! Where's the harm
in them thinking that way?
Who cares about that?!
I don't think you have to boot
them off of the Ten for
simply disagreeing!
Rindo Kobayashi quite
vocally disagreed
[RINDO] I mean, come on!
with that particular
ruling of mine.
[RINDO] They're good chefs!
Are you serious?
I mean I take it
you won't be getting rid of
your daughter, will you?
I know that, in time,
she will return to my side.
I'm sure she will come around
to agree with my thinking.
[AZAMI] And now, thanks to you,
there is much to do.
The Food Wars, you mean?
Yes. I've confirmed that you've
made the necessary arrangements.
According to these rules,
that is.
These research societies and
Seminars we wish to abolish
must now be challenged...
by the pride that is Central's
corps of soldiers.
[MOMO] "Regarding the rules that
research societies and seminars
engaging in Food Wars to
challenge their dissolution,
also now presently known as
'The Isshiki Rules,' will..."
Now wait, just a second.
He's named it after himself?
That pisses me off.
Yes, well, by clearly stating
that he will have absolutely
no interaction with
the judges at all,
Isshiki has made sure that
the rulings will be fair
from here on out.
And I'm glad he made
that happen, too.
I was against that sort of thing
from the start.
Correct me if I'm wrong here,
but doesn't that clause state,
"any Food War contesting
a group's dissolution
MUST be accepted"?
That Isshiki,
he's covering his bases.
[gah]
But now we're going to have to
battle all these stupid losers,
and that pisses me off, too.
I did take the overall
top-spot in the Lunar Feast,
so I think I should win by
default no matter what.
Please accept this rule,
Chef Momo.
Also, Chef Rindo,
if you would please be sure
to wear your badge from Central.
[RINDO] Whaaat?
But that thing's such a pain.
Come on, girl.
[NENE]
There's no "Whaat?" about it.
[RINDO] But still-
[NENE]
There's no "But, still" either.
Just do it.
Fine! Everyone, be sure to
put your badges on,
or Nene will get in
a big 'ol tizzy.
Yeah, you don't have to
tell me twice.
[RINDO] Well,
I guess we should head out.
It's time to go hunt
some stragglers.
[SOMA] "Hunting the stragglers"?
Apparently, that's what Central
has decided to call it
when someone challenges their
disbandment through a Food War.
So far, this would be
the first instance.
Really?
Has kind of a bad ring to it.
It looks like Central's members
will be the ones carrying
this thing out.
Yes, the ones following Azami.
As well as the Ten's
"Reserve Army" of skilled chefs.
[SOMA]
Whoa, a reserve army, huh?
I'd like to see what kind
of guys they are.
[ALL] Huh?!
It looks like he's
up to something again.
Don't go off and get
into more trouble!
[TAKUMI]
If you're going to go watch a
Food War, I'll go with you.
You being out there on your own
will just make us all worry.
Having them there will
help us rest easy.
[RYOKO] Yeah, well,
kinda feels like they're always
here at the dorm anyway.
[GUYS] (arguing)
U-uh, I'd like to go too!
I mean it looks like Regional
Cuisine is also doing
a Food War.
My Miyazato Seminar will be
battling today as well.
It'd be a shame not to go
and support them.
Apparently, they've divided the
Food Wars into three venues.
Then, I say we should split into
groups and go watch all of them!
Yeah, let's do it!
So, I think we should go
and watch the A Venue.
Sounds terrific!
Okay,
I guess we take Venue B, B!
But I'm really worried about
leaving Ms Erina for so long...
Knockers babe will be just fine!
I mean, Ms Fumio will be here-
[HISAKO]
Stop calling her knockers babe!
I-I'm sorry!
All right! Then that means
we're headed to C Venue!
Okay, Soma, today we're
only going to observe.
Don't take things too far,
understand?
Yeah, yeah, I know, man.
I don't know about
"straggler hunting",
but as long as I'm drawing
breath, I will allow
no tomfoolery!
Indeed. It's our responsibility
to deliver an honest judgment.
Whoa,
there's a lot going on here.
Let's see, right now...
No. 4 Chef Momo vs.
Chocolate Research Society.
[TAKUMI]
Chef Eizan vs. the Western
Cuisine Research Society.
It's looking like they're going
to hold multiple Food Wars
within the same venue,
should be interesting.
I don't see the guys from
Bowl-Soc anywhere.
Or even Akira from
Shiomi Seminar.
Here we go, Pucchi.
Help me out with my cooking,
'kay?
[ALL] (uh...)
Okeedokee...
Let's see how it turned out.
She just used the hands from her
stuffed doll as mittens.
Is there some reason for
her doing that?
They say that she pulls that
move every time she's
in a Food War!
[TAKUMI]
Sure enough, she moves fast.
They say she's Totsuki Academy's
top patissier.
Yeah, that cake she made
for the autumn-leaf viewing
was SUPER delicious!
All done!
It's beautiful...
But how will it taste?
[cheering]
[ANNOUNCER] Momo Akanegakubo
and Etsuya Eizan,
both have achieved
flawless victories!
[MEGUMI] Incredible!
Central completely
dominated the matches.
Oh...
I'd like to battle them too.
Soma, stop!
[TAKUMI] Um, Soma...
Not to belabor the point, but
today we're only here for recon.
You are NOT to cha-
Yeah, yeah, I know, I get it!
Soma Yukihira!
Speaking of which, I haven't
seen what your true specialty
is yet, Chef Eizan.
We should come up with a dish
and have a knock-down,
drag-out Food War.
Y'know one day, for real?
[agh!] Dammit!
There's no way I can let
things end like this.
I will do whatever it takes
to make him pay for
embarrassing me!
Goodness he's so worked up!
And this coming from somebody
who couldn't possibly hack it
on the Ten.
Looks like it's time
to pass the baton!
Leave the Food Wars to us,
Mr. "I Lost to a First Year."
Better luck next time!
[oohs and aahs]
Those guys are the troops
of Azami Nakiri,
specially brought for Central.
They're on the side of those
who'll be governing Totsuki.
So, you're really okay
with this? You want us
to choose the theme?
Of course. All four of us
will gladly battle you
with the cooking style in which
you and your teammates excel.
We're gonna use the genre
you've worked so hard
to try and perfect
and annihilate you with it.
Well that's not very nice.
Going out of your way to try
to humiliate your opponent...
Oh come on, that's what
makes winning so much FUN
in this place!
Don't you think, Chef Momo?
[SPANISH HEAD] You can make
fun of us all you like.
But you're right in one thing.
We HAVE worked extremely hard
here at Totsuki.
We will not be intimidated.
[cheers]
Now, choose.
Are you going to be a good boy
and disband your little club,
or do you want to get tossed
out of Totsuki never
to be seen again?
We will disband our
research club.
[hmph!]
None of these guys
are a challenge! Ha!
Do you get it now?
You are not the chosen ones.
So obey us!
It's the right thing to do!
All of you, bow your heads to
those of us at Central!
It's the only option you've got!
[manaical laugh]
[BOTH]
We CANNOT let that slide!
Hmm? What?!
Huh? Did you first years
say something to me?
We're saying we have a lot
more to offer than you're
giving us credit for.
And we cannot stand here and
allow that to happen!
Now it's not just Soma,
but Takumi too?!
You're the first-year
who defeated Eizan.
And if I'm not mistaken you were
also in the Fall Selection?
You'd do well not to take
that nasty attitude here.
Not with me, the ELITE who'll be
heading up the next generation.
The "Elite"?
[KUSUNOKI] That's right.
We are the elite,
specifically chosen by the
current director of this school.
It'd be in your best interests
not to oppose us.
I'm not getting a real sense
of identity from you.
[KUSUNOKI] Huh?
Stressing how you've been
"chosen" and all that.
It makes you sound like you're
hiding an inferiority complex
or something.
If you have to build yourself up
by repeatedly saying you're
some kind of elite chef,
doesn't that mean you don't have
much confidence in your
cooking skills?
[squeal of horror]
That's a pretty smart thing
you said. Not bad.
What do you say to that,
huh, Chef?
Oh, you're asking for it.
I'm gonna crush you,
right here and now- [huh?!]
Don't make a fool of yourself.
It's sad.
Shige! Put me down! Hey!
[KUMAI] You're making it worse.
Okay, okay, I get it!
I'll do what you say! I promise!
[BOTH] (huh...)
You get bent outta shape
too easily, Renni boy!
Shut up, Mea!
You damn 1st-Years!
Just you wait!
You ARE going down!
I MEAN IT!
Yeah, yeah, just be on your way.
And come up with your
final match already.
Huh? That dude?
He's doing the next battle too?
Who's the challenger?
[gasp]
[students chattering]
[SOMA] Alice Nakiri... and Ryo!
Hi!
Nice to see you both here today.
Why are you two here?
[TAKUMI]
Did you join a research society?
It was quite surprising
actually!
When I was in the
middle school division,
I did a Food War against the
Cutting Edge Culinary
Research Society.
I won, of course. So I went
ahead and took their club room
and all their equipment.
Then recently, I got a notice
that I had become their
new club's chief!
An obvious choice I'm sure.
That seems kinda cold.
Oh!
That's why they came after you,
for this hunting thing?
[giggle] But of course!
So feel free to call me "Chief
Alice," from now on, boys!
[TAKUMI] Even though you didn't
know this whole time?
[SOMA] But if that's the case,
why don't you just disband
the group and avoid the fight?
[ALICE] (sigh) Yeah, well,
here's the thing about that...
[KUSUNOKI] So then, Cutting
Edge-Soc will be disbanded,
or I could go ahead and
battle you in a Food War,
if that's what you would
prefer to do.
[ALICE] Oh, sure, do whatever
you feel like doing.
[KUSUNOKI] Huh?
The title of "Chief"
is a new one for me,
and I'm a little sad to see it
go, but I don't really care.
Would you please leave?
[KUSUNOKI] (wha?)
That's smart. Just stay quiet
and watch the Azami
Administration at work.
You pansy-ass little chefs
need to stay in your lane.
WHO'RE YOU CALLIN' A PANSY ASS,
HUH?!
Whoa! Hey, what got into him?
[RYO] Anyone who comes for me,
I'll chew 'em up and
spit 'em out!
I got half a mind to stab you
in your pathetic heart
with my cooking!
Okay, very well.
We will accept your Food War.
And so, now, it will be Ryo
who does all the fighting!
I think it's about time, Ryo.
Go expose this elf-styled,
wannabe "elite"
what he's gotten himself into.
[RYO] Gotcha!
So who will be in the final
Food War of C-Venue on
the first day?
Ryo Kurokiba!
[SAOTOME] "The Despot of the
Kitchen," Ryo Kurokiba,
versus the rookie from Central,
Rentaro Kusunoki!
Hey, Ryo! Don't you dare lose!
And that is a direct order from
the Chief of the Cutting Edge
club! Do you hear me?!
Not today. We cannot let Uncle
Azami do whatever he likes.
Ryo Kurokiba...
I saw that you somehow made it
to the finals in the
Fall Selection.
There was an incident
a bit earlier that kinda
pissed me off.
So, I'll be sure to take
that out on YOU today.
You're not a bad opponent
to have the pleasure of
forcing into submission
on the first day.
[RYO] If you think you're gonna
force me into submission...
Then get ready to have that crap
thrown right back in your face!
[music playing]
Good luck, Ryo!
We'll be here watching! Okay?!
Yeah, sorry 'bout
all the yelling.
We hope you don't mind us here
in the front row making
a bunch of noise!
[hmph!]
[SOMA] (huh)
[MEA] Ah, that's just
Chef Momo's default mode,
so I wouldn't worry
too much about it.
It takes about a month for her
to make eye contact,
or even bother to talk to you.
Huh? So, then, how in the
world did you make it
through the training camp,
or even through the Stagiaire?
What reason would I ever have
for discussing something
like that with YOU?
You're pathetic.
[SOMA] Huh? What's that?
Soma! You're being too
forceful with her!
[ANNOUNCER]
The theme ingredient is salmon!
Oh, that's some good salmon.
The color and the luster
are first-rate.
So fish?
C'mon Ryo!
Just concentrate and do it!
[ANNOUNCER]
It's Rentaro Kusunoki
versus Ryo Kurokiba!
This friggin' Food War battle...
starts NOW!