[VENDOR A] Have a taste!
[VENDOR B] Step right up!
Hya! Hya! Hya! Hya!
[YUKI] Whoa!
It's just like I've heard!
China-Soc looks pretty
formidable over there.
How about some hujiao bing?
I've got "Kinda Sorta
Danzi Noodles" too.
Hey, Yuki and Ryoko!
Why are you here?
What about the hotpot party?
We're supposed to take our
breaks in shifts now.
More importantly, are you guys
still in the red?!
Well, um, we have a new item,
"Kinda Sorta Danzi Noodles"
on the menu,
so our sales are
definitely up now.
But we lost so much our first
day that we still haven't-
Are you for real?!
[KUGA] Hey, Soma!
[SOMA] Huh?
Oh, what's up, Chef Kuga?
Care to try out a hujiao bing?
[KUGA] No thanks!
So, hey, I hear you've been out
and about scurrying around
at all hours.
It's nice that you've
fleshed out the menu a bit,
but it's already day three.
Your struggling business out in
front of my establishment
is proofing to be
a bit of an eyesore.
Would you mind just
closing up your shop?
Like just close it up right now!
My whole life, I'll never forget
that you were here!
So, c'mon! Don't just walk,
run and close up shop.
Do it! Just get out!
Beat it, right now!
C'mon, c'mon! You can do it!
It's not hard!
C'mon, c'mon, c'mon, c'mon!
That's making me so angry!
[KUGA] Shutter those doors!
[MAN] Whoa, look at this line!
What kinda shop is this?
I heard it's Sichuan cusine.
You wanna try?
Oh? Hello there!
Sorry, but please move to the
very back of the line, 'kay?
We at Kuga Chinese Restaurant
are waiting to serve you
with all our heart!
I don't know why Soma
would do this to himself
and take on a challenge he's
got no chance of winning?
He's just way too reckless.
Not that this is anything
new of course.
You know, Soma said
something yesterday.
[Both] (huh)
[MEGUMI] About China-Soc:
Do you think EVERYTHING about
their shop is 100% perfect
all of the time?
So, you know...
But I mean...
Look at how much traffic
they're getting!
Even so...
Soma keeps going.
He hasn't given up.
[music playing]
Hya! Hya! Hya! Hya!
[whoops of delight]
[SOMA] For real?
[laughing]
That's a big help!
Yeah, thanks for doing this,
Tomita!
Okay, he's agreed to
get things ready for us.
Next, I think I'd like to get a
whole bunch of you know what,
because what we have isn't
gonna cut it anymore.
I might be able to do
something about that.
You just keep working
on your dish, all right.
Yeah!
Ah! Hello, Master?
That you?
I have a favor to ask, if I can.
I'm finished.
Soma, you're amazing!
With this,
you might be able to...
Yeah! Let's go do this!
Tomorrow's Saturday.
We're gonna have more
visitors than ever.
It's perfect!
[KUGA] Good morning, gentlemen!
Yesterday, we of China-Soc
once again got first place
in earnings!
You have my gratitude.
Let's give it our all
again today!
We got this!
[MEMBERS] Sir!
[KUGA] (sigh)
Just two more days, Tsukasa.
I am the Mysterious
Soup Dumpling Man!
And I am the Mysterious
Skewered Chicken Meatball Man!
And I am Mysterious
Assorment of Sashimi Man!
[TRIO]
The Tohtsuki Masked Rangers:
Gastron!
[GASTRON RED]
Stand back, mysterious men
of foul cuisine!
Gastron, yeah! You're so cool!
So awesome! They've the
legendary cooking manga
"Knife-kun Akiro"!
The whole series,
in first editions!
That's SUPER rare!
[WOMAN] That smells wonderful!
[MAN] Oh, I love this!
[BOY] It's so yummy!
[MAN] That's awesome!
[WOMAN] One, please.
[WOMAN 2] Me too!
[WOMAN 3] It's nice and hot!
[WOMAN 4] What an aroma!
[TEEN] This rocks!
[GUY] IT'S LIKE FIRE!
[WOMAN] So spicy!
But it's incredible!
Hya! Hya! Hya! Hya!
[MEMBER] Um, Master Kuga!
You should see this.
Hmm?
[MEGUMI] Wow...
[SOMA] (chuckling) All right!
Thanks! Sorry for all
the trouble, man.
No problem,
happy to do it for you.
Besides, they were just
sitting in the arcade's
storage room anyway.
But you know, that shop over is
on a whole different level.
You really think benches
will do the trick?
Totally!
These are great!
In fact, let me make you
something to eat!
It's my way of saying thanks!
Oh, you mean it?!
It's been so long since
I've had your food!
I'm always ready for the flavors
of some "Yukihira" cooking!
Not too creative,
is it, Soma?
[SOMA] (huh?)
THIS is the best you could come
up with when challenging me?
Expecting guests to come just
because you've put out more
chairs is a little too naive,
even for you, don't you think?
You will never be able to
equal me in pure taste.
Although it may be true,
this is my first Lunar Fest.
After all, I just barely
transferred here
six months ago.
But when it comes to setting up
shop and running a business,
you better believe I'm YOUR
senior by about a good
10 years, Chef Kuga!
What?
Is this guy really doing this?
[MEMBER 2] Mapo tofu!
I can't believe he's actually
challenging Terunori Kuga
head-on with mapo tofu?!
Hey, Soma! Here ya go!
[SOMA] Okay!
[MEMBER 3]
He added NOODLES to it!
Mapo noodles? Well, he may have
changed things up a little bit,
but I mean, that hardly
makes it a new dish!
If he really thinks THAT has
enough impact to take on
China-Soc,
he's in for a rude awakening.
[MEMBER]
[MEMBER 4] What's that?!
[MEMBER 2]
It's a giant meatball!
It's like I told you earlier...
I'm going to beat
you with my cooking!
[humphf!] Let's go.
There's nothing special about
some ball of meat!
It may have lots of style
but it garners no substance!
It's ridiculous!
That meatball...
Here you go, Tomita.
Thank you very much!
Oh wow!
What did you make here, Soma?
Oh, you'll see. First,
I want you to try some of it
without breaking up
the meatball.
[TOMITA] Oh, okay.
[slurping]
[shocked] Now this is the
"Yukihira," I've been missing!
Their mapo tofu!
The flavor's so good,
so balanced,
I could eat it every day!
These noodles make
the perfect addition.
That Soma's a genius!
But...
[KUGA] Sorry for the wait!
Here's your Kuga
Chinese Restaurant
Super Deluxe,
Authentic Mapo Tofu!
[MAN] SO SPICY!
[MAN 2] My face is on fire!
[WOMAN] Help! I can't stop!
There's no way he can
go up against THAT.
That guy is unbeatable!
His cooking style is
just too powerful!
[SOMA] I'm not so sure...
[TOMITA] What?
Keeping your customers 100%
satisfied is hard to do.
Something can go wrong even for
a pro with decades under him.
[MAN] I'm tired of waiting...
[WOMAN] We haven't moved yet.
How much longer until we were
finally able to go inside?
Excuse me, sir, when the
restaurant is this crowded,
we ask that you please give up
your seat within
20 minutes of eating.
What? But I just barely
finished eating my meal!
The line just keeps going.
I wanted to try some authentic
Sichuan cuisine, but geez...
I'm hungry, mama!
[MAN] Still nothing?!
[WOMAN] I'm tired of waiting!
[BOY] Mom, I'm starving!
[WOMAN 2]
I'm just about done with this!
[MAN] I wanna EAT!
[WOMAN 3] I have had it!
[TOMITA] Ah...
[discontented crowd]
[SOMA] I've been watching
this whole time,
but until today, I wasn't
able to find it:
the flaw of
Kuga Chinese Restaurant.
Hey, Tomita, would you please
dunk that meatball into the
mapo tofu and break it up.
Oh, yeah, okay.
I'll just smoosh this a little,
and...
[whoosh!]
[BOTH] (shocked!)
[crowd notices smell]
[evil chuckle]
[TOMITA] It's the Moon!
I see the MOON!
This heavenly aroma...
I'm absolutely positive!
It's curry! That savory
fragrance that always brings
a smile to everyone's face!
What kind of dish is that?
Is that curry in mapo tofu?!
I've never tried
anything like that!
[TOMITA]
That "Moon" continues to melt,
blending with the mapo tofu.
Well, that should
just about do it.
I'd say it's the best time
to eat, if I were you.
Enjoy, my friend!
[slurping]
[joyous laughter]
What is this deliciousness?!
It's aromatic and spicy,
stimulating but with
a gentle smoothness.
It's enveloping my body
and seeping into my bones!
It's like Soma has invented
a whole new style
of Chinese food!
The soup is made
with beef bones,
along with select spices
of garlic and ginger,
which are put into a broth
to ultimately make that
curry flavor
creating the "Moon" inside.
The broth is thickened with
gelatin and wrapped in
a hujiao patty
that's delicately fried.
The meat won't fall apart,
and the curry flavor slowly
seeps into the mapo.
This is the "Yukihira No. 2,
Limited Edition
Mapo Curry Noodles"!
That sounds
freakin' awesome, man!
All this aroma...
I can't take it!
Right? So good!
Oh, man!
[crowd getting exicted]
[MAN] Let's go over there!
Our customers!
He took 'em away!
The guy just stole
more than half of them!
[KUGA] Calm down. There's no way
some pissant little
rickety stall
can meet that kind
of high demand!
It's all bound to blow up
in his face at any minute.
[SOMA] Welcome!
[MEGUMI] Here,
hope you enjoy it!
That meat patty, from the
ingredients to how it was put
together, it's pretty clever.
But it's a lot like a noodle
dish eaten in Taiwan
and on the Mainland...
And that is called Shizitou!
The giant ball of meat on top
is supposed to represent
a lion's head.
By rights, you're little more
than a feeble housecat,
but in just two days since
your initial loss...
[ROAR
You have become a fierce lion!
But don't think that's enough
to bring you a victory over me,
little Soma.
For we are many,
and you are but TWO!
No matter how you look at it,
there's no way you can win!
[IKUMI]
Ultra-premium beef bowls,
order of six, up and ready!
Hey, Meat-Meat! At this rate,
we might just be able-
Yeah! We have the chance to
take first place in our area!
Trippa alla Fiorentina,
your order is up!
Thanks for waiting.
Please enjoy!
Three mapo curry noodles!
And I'd like a couple, please!
Coming right up!
[LADY]
Gimme a mapo curry noodle!
[MAN] Two hujiao bing and
one of those danzi noodles!
[MAN 2]
I'll take a hujiao bing too.
[WOMAN] Oh, um,
two mapo curries, please.
[MAN 3] Can I get one
of those danzi noodles?
I bet you're just about to
break, my little, Soma.
[MEGUMI] Oh, god!
[clamoring for food]
I don't think I can keep up with
all the orders anymore, Soma!
I'd say it's about that time.
Huh? Time for what?
[MEGUMI] (startled gasp)
So, on that day,
when everything counts,
I'd like to enlist your help.
It doesn't look like you'll
be putting up your own shop,
so can I count on you for this?
I'll need to do some type
of visual training.
That will speed things up a lot
for when the time comes.
It's far more effective
for me to do it
in the same environment as
the person I'll be copying.
I'll need to borrow
your kitchen.
That's just like you, Mimasaka.
Sure.
Thanks, again.
And here ya go.
[SOMA] I'm counting on you.
[MAYUMI] Um, is anybody here?
[frightened]
Order is up!
Thank you!
One mapo tofu?
Sure, coming right up!
Soma Yukihira's the name.
I'm gonna have to show
Chef Kuga what's what!
And I'm 10 years more senior
than that Chef Kuga twerp!
Why didn't you just
say that from the start?
That guy's the No. 4 best
from the Fall Selection!
[MEMBER 2] It's Mimasaka!
[scoffing] So he has one more
person helping him, so what?
You made sure to memorize that
recipe I gave you yesterday,
yeah?
Don't start questioning my
perfect copying abilities now.
I'm about to show you the
results of ALL MY YEARS
of dedicated visual training.
Okay! In that case...
[BOTH] Kuga Chinese Restaurant
eat your words!
Hya! Hya! Hya! Hya!
I need an order of
Mapo Curry Noodles for 10!
[BOTH] Yeah! Got it!
[TOMITA] Amazing! That big guy
over there is able to move just
as lightening quick as Soma!
[BOTH] Order is up!
I don't believe it!
It's as if...
there are now TWO
Soma Yukihiras!
[MAN] This is great!
[WOMAN] It's delicious!
You really helped me out,
big time, Mimaska.
I appreciate you getting
me through all this.
It's because I have a
great debt that I owe you.
[SOMA] Wait, what was that?
It's nothing. This is no for us
time to stand around and talk!
We've got more customers coming!
[WOMAN] Hujiao Bing
looks tasty, doesn't it?
[BOY] Mommy, let's get this!
[OLD MAN] I'll take three!
Megumi, help me out.
[MEGUMI] Sure!
[MEGUMI]
Please have a seat over here.
[OLD MAN] Oh, thank you.
[MEGUMI]
Would you prefer to use a spoon?
[MOM] Ah, yes, I would.
Thank you very much!
[MEGUMI] There should be plenty
of room for your stroller here.
[MAN
Ah, thank you. That's great!
[TOMITA] She's so good
with the customers!
This girl's incredible!
Thanks for everything.
That was yummy!
That looks wonderful.
What the customers want
is to know which
dishes are heavy
and which are light before
deciding on which one to order.
I'm using everything
I learned at the Stagiaire!
[BOTH] OH, YEAH!
And then it just hit me!
It's going to be great!
[hm?]
What, exactly, just "hit" you?
I will need to do
some prep work.
Ryo, come with me. Come on!
[RYO] Okay.
Ah, where are you going?
Go ahead and make the curry,
Akira!
And use some spices that are
a good fit for cacao!
[AKIRA] What? Cacao? But...
Hey, Alice!
[exasperated sigh]
Get a move on, Ryo.
[RYO] 'kay.
[SOMA] It should be
getting dark pretty soon.
Yeah, sorry.
I don't think it'll be too long.
[MASTER] Megumi!
Sorry to keep you waiting.
[MEGUMI] Master!
[MASTER] Go ahead and set
them all up, please.
The Regional Cuisine Society
is proud to bring you
our prized collection of
lanterns from across Japan!
[MEMBERS] (cheering)
[GIRL] So pretty...
[WOMAN] They're lovely,
aren't they?
[GIRL 2] Wow!
[crowd approves]
Look at that one! It says
"Jiufen," like in Taiwan.
Oh my gosh, it totally makes me
want to eat some hujiao bing!
Thank you for setting
all of this up for us.
They're so beautiful!
Even after I said I couldn't
help with your own booth.
I must admit I was very
surprised to hear you
passed on helping us out.
But I knew there must be a
pretty good reason
for you to do so.
I know you take this
seriously,
and you're not the type to
back out of something lightly.
Thank you, sir!
I appreciate that.
[WOMAN] What's with
all those lanterns?
[WOMAN 2] Let's go take a look.
[MAN] Something smells good!
[OLD LADY] Is one "Pickled Plum"
ticket enough?
[MEGUMI]
Yes, but you'll have to wait
a bit for the hujiao bing.
[MAN]
One order of noodles, please!
[MEGUMI] Okay, coming up!
I'll have a mapo curry noodle.
[OLD LADY] One Kinda Sorta Danzi
Noodle bowl, please.
[MEGUMI] Sure!
Everyone please stay in line.
I'm really sorry!
Sure enough, it's gotten
kinda tough with just the
three of us working.
But we have to
keep going, or else
China-Soc will roll right
over us like we're nothing.
Hey, hey, hey!
What seems to be the trouble
over there, little Soma?
Come on, don't you get it?
No matter how many
customers you get,
at that pace,
you'll never beat me!
Hya! Hya! Hya! Hya!
Excuse me, please!
Can someone come over here
and clear this table?
Okay, I'll be right there!
Two mapo curry noodles, please!
I'm still waiting on
my hujiao bing?
[MEGUMI] Ah! One moment, please!
Megumi's doing too much.
I'll have to go cook up
the hujiao bing.
I've gotta leave this to you!
You big dumb idiot!
If you step away from
that stove now,
you're throwing away
your chance at winning!
Megumi, you tend to
the customers.
As for the hujiao bing...
I'll handle that.
[MEGUMI] Wait, what?!
Meat-Meat!
What about Bowl-Soc?
I left that to the youngsters.
And when it comes
to hujiao bing,
I've tasted one of these
things before.
So you don't have to
explain the recipe to me!
[IKUMI]
When cooking the hujiao bing,
you need to make sure the
exterior is crispy
but not burned.
That's the best way to have all
the meaty juices rest in the
face of that flickering flame.
It's where the flavors
come together.
That way you can
do it perfectly,
even with your eyes closed.
[gasp]
Some fresh baked hujiao bing!
Eat up!
Meat-Meat, thanks a lot!
[MEGUMI] Thanks so much
for your help!
[gleeful laugh] These two have
worked together before,
in our shopping arcade!
When she joins the fight,
she's a force you know
you can count on!
[TAKUMI] AHEM! It would seem
you're having a little
trouble, Soma.
I cannot sit idly by!
Very well!
I mean, if you insist.
I am not averse to lending you
this winning hand of mine!
Yeah, and I'll go boil
the noodles for you.
That'd be a big help to me!
Now, hold on, Isami!
Listen to me, Soma.
This is Terunori Kuga
you've just challenged.
And there's no way I can allow
you to go down like this,
not without a fight.
[SOMA] (chuckles)
Well then, it's
do-or-die time, Takumi.
You wanna come with?
[TAKUMI] A foolish question!
Aldini...
It took me a long time
to be this fast.
But look at him.
He's doing it so easily.
What's wrong over there,
Mimasaka?
You're looking pretty slow!
Shut up!
I'm just getting started!
Huh!
I'll believe it when I see it!
In the end, THIS has become
a GREAT restaurant.
[happy chatter]
I get it.
So then, Soma Yukihira,
it took you four days,
but you've finally
completed your restaurant?!
It's almost time to
tally up the sales.
Just one hour left.
It's the last spurt, guys!
Let's do this!
[ALL] Yeah!
Just watching is such an
emotional experience...
[KANICHI] (gaaah!)
They got me all emotional!
[TOMITA] Hm?
[KANICHI] Hm?
[BOTH] I can't help but think
I know this person.
[chimes]
[YUME] And now, the sales
rankings for the Central Area.
In third place, from the Spanish
Cuisine Research Society,
is "El Fuego."
In second place...
China-Soc's
"Kuga Chinese Restaurant."
[MEMBERS] (shocked)
[grrr...] Damn you, Soma,
you WILL PAY FOR THIS!
[URARA] And in first place is...
Soma Yukihira with his
little stall!
We did it, guys!
You did it, Soma!
I can't believe it, Soma!
Guess this means you're not
in the red anymore.
You were pretty great
out there, Mimasaka.
Yeah, right back at ya, Aldini.
[ALL] You're welcome, everyone!
[cheering and clapping
[music playing]
[WOMAN] Wow, so pretty!
What is that on top of
the curry there?
Is that really chocolate?
[giggle] Yes, it is!
And it was made using these
3D food printers over here!
[WOMAN]
Huh? Food from a printer?
Yes! It's 80% cacao chocolate
mixed with spices and
rendered in the machines.
Let me explain how
the chocolate works.
When used as a topping,
it slowly melts into the curry,
changing the flavor profile to
give it more "brightness"!
[WOMAN 2] It smells so
wonderful, like the curry
itself is going to melt!
[GIRL] Daddy! Buy me one!
[MAN] I want one too!
[MAN 2] Give me a bowl!
[MAN 3] I'll take three!
People like it, and a wide
range of customers too.
[giggle] This single item has
totally turned things around.
And we'll be going up
in the rankings.
At this rate,
we'll turn a profit.
Yes! But more than anything,
we've actually made the
customers happy.
Thank goodness, right?!
Here ya go.
[OLD LADY]
Is mine ready yet, dear?
Oh, it's coming right up!
Sorry for the wait, madam.
Didn't see that coming.
[ALICE]
From a "Pine Tree" ticket?
Oh, Akira, you're smiling!
You're getting along
with your friends.
That makes me so very
happy to see!
[ERINA] Hisako...
All the guests have
arrived, correct?
Yes, Ms Erina.
All but one, of course.
I made sure to once again
leave one of our tables
empty for tonight,
and in a prime location.
Thank you.
[ERINA] It's "just-in-case."