[URARA] And in first place is...
Soma Yukihira with
his little stall!
[RINDO] Seriously, Kuga,
you actually LOST!
This is unbelievable. (chuckle)
[music playing]
[wails of despair]
Soma...
Dammit!
And I was so close!
[RINDO] Kuga! KUGA!
Look at you! You got outsold!
You loser!
Oh god! It had to be her!
That's the No. 2 Seat!
[SOMA] (huh?)
You are a hair shy of useless,
aren't you?
Well, Kuga? Huh? Yeah?!
Shut up already!
I don't wanna hear this
from someone who just
walked around eating
and didn't even participate
in the Lunar Feast!
What are you talking about?
Walking around and eating is
the best way of participating.
And whatever.
Isn't staying holed up
in your restaurant
the very reason you got beaten
by your JUNIOR over there?
Shut up, shut up,
shut up, shut up!
Chef Kuga's getting a
verbal smackdown.
She seems almost like his
older sister or something.
[KUGA] Still, yeah,
you're right, I lost.
And I'm pretty sure it was all
part of little Soma's devious
master plan the whole time.
Soon, we'll hold a Food War to-
And why's that?
There's still one day left
till the Feast ends, right?
[RINDO] (hmm?)
[KUGA] What?
[SOMA] We're not done yet.
You have to win by making
the most money in FIVE days.
This battle's just
getting started, Kuga!
[sizzle!]
[RINDO] Hard at work,
aren't you, Soma Yukihira?
Still, at this rate, I doubt
you'll be able to sell enough
to win against Kuga though.
Well, at least you got close.
Actually,
what I had in mind was...
to basically duke it out
till Day 3,
beat him silly on Day 4,
and then win in overall sales
on the last day, cementing his
doom! (wicked cackle).
Sounds pretty na ve,
if you ask me.
[SOMA] I thought for sure I had
a pretty good chance of winning,
and I had no intention of
being beaten when it came
to hospitality.
So this stings... for real.
You have no problem speaking
your mind, do ya?
[girly squeals of excitement]
[cheers and sobbing]
[RINDO] (whooo!)
This is even tastier
than last year, Kuga.
You remember that
Fall Leaf-Viewing Festival?
I gotta tell ya, I seriously
almost burst out laughing!
I never thought there'd be
someone else who says the same
sorts of kooky things as you.
So, uh, I'd prefer to join
the Ten, like, right now.
Would one of you guys be
interested in doing a
Food War with me?
Why would we bother to do that?!
[KUGA] Um....
I have no interest in
forging any friendships
or engaging in idle chitchat,
so...
Would one of folks you mind
doing a Food War with me?
What are you talking about,
you moron?
You can't just come in here
and challenge the Ten-
[TSUKASA] Sure.
Today even, if you like.
If I will do, that is.
Sound good?
[drum beats]
[KUGA]
I mean, come on, after all,
we 2nd-years are SUPER busy
trying to take down our
seniors as well.
As I remember,
at last year's school festival
you got top sales in the Central
Area for five days straight,
right, Tsukasa?
So, make me a promise
if you would:
If I'm able to go out there and
pull off the same thing you did
in this year's Lunar Feast...
You and I will do
another Food War.
But in the end, things didn't
go as you had hoped.
And Soma Yukihira didn't
get top sales.
My goodness, that, my friend,
is what they would call a war
with no victor.
You both look so upset
you could just DIE.
Shut up. Anyway, I suspect Soma
is only going to get better
with time.
[laughing] So you've just
accepted the inevitable?
Like hell I have!
I've taken an interest too,
in our young Soma Yukihira.
[MEGUMI] We've used up most
of our ingredients.
[SOMA] We had great sales
on our last day as well.
We were so close...
[RINDO] Hey, Soma!
The table's being set tonight,
yeah?
Huh? The table?
[RINDO] In the Mountain Area.
You're coming, aren't you?
[SOMA] (ummm...)
[RINDO] Huh? Where's Mimasaka?
He had to break in somewhere
with tighter security than
usual, so he left earlier.
Sounds like it's a lot of work
getting to his level
of mastery.
All right, you two,
finish things up.
Close your stall and
we'll all go together.
We'll dine at
Eishi Tsukasa's shop.
[BOTH] (huh?)
[RINDO] I'm sure you're curious
what kind of food the current
No. 1 Seat makes.
So then, let's hurry up and
our butts to the Mountain Area!
AWESOME! What is all this?!
[MEGUMI] We're in the
Mountain Area, all right!
Compared to the other areas,
it's like we're in a whole
different world!
Everyone is busy closing up
their shops over in the
Central Area,
but things are still up
and running strong here, huh?
It's the difference
in clientele.
Most of them either live on
premises or are staying at
the Totsuki Resort.
That's why a lot of the
restaurants here do a prix fixe
dinner around this time.
That's going to be super
expensive, right?!
Oh, don't you worry,
my sweet Megumi.
I'll be picking up the tab
at Tsukasa's place, all right?
Oh, wait, that's right.
Isn't this the area where
Isshiki and other members
of the Ten
usually have their shops
set up for the festival?
[EIZAN] And sales were good?
Great. Go ahead and send
my production fee
to the usual account,
if you wouldn't mind.
[chuckle]
Whaaa? Chef Eizan managed
TWENTY of the food stalls
in the Lunar Feast?!
Yep!
And he made a boatload of cash.
That's like, way more than a
student should be doing.
So, what were YOU up to
during all of this?
[hmm] Oh, nothing much.
[SOMA & MEGUMI] What?! You went
to all 120 shops in five days?!
Tsukasa's restaurant made the
list complete.
It was a lot of work!
But was all that "hard work"
really worth it in the end?
Sure enough, the Ten is made up
of a bunch of monsters.
What are you two
doing back there?
You're gonna get left behind!
[WAITER] Welcome, Ms Kobayashi.
Tonight's theme is
"A Fall Symphony,"
which consists of an exceptional
nine-course menu.
Please,
make yourself comfortable.
It's like he's on stage.
Everything around Chef Tsukasa
seems like a fantasy!
So, there are only three tables
being served?
[RINDO] Tsukasa does all of
the cooking himself.
Everyone else is just waitstaff.
He's gotta try and keep
everything small,
or else his particular
restaurant concept would
never work out.
You mean to say he does nine
courses all by himself?
He must be incredibly
confident in himself,
or none of this
would be possible!
Actually, the real reason he
does what he does is simple.
[TSUKASA] The thought of leaving
the food up to someone else
is terrifying!
When I imagine them
making a mistake,
it's impossible for me to
concentrate on my own cooking!
[wail]
[soft music playing]
[TSUKASA]
These are ready to serve.
And PLEASE, I beg you,
make sure that you preserve
the plating exactly as it is!
Whatever you do, carry it
gently, ever so gently!
Uh... understood.
What the? These are...
Sakura shrimp, right?
But they're in season in SPRING.
Yeah, but they said this would
use fall ingredients...
[chuckle of anticipation]
[MEGUMI] (huh?)
[aahhh...]
[orgasmic chuckle]
[MEGUMI] (AAHHH!)
[RINDO] (oh, yes!)
That's Tsukasa for you,
all right!
Sakura shrimp may be widely
associated with spring,
but in fact, they surprisingly
grow larger in the fall,
and develop even more depth
of flavor than we're used to!.
And that's why he used them?
Because he knew that!
Unreal!
It's like the ingredients in
all his dishes shine and "pop"
even more than in
their original state!
And the way this menu
is laid out,
any dish with lots of acidity
is followed by something
slightly sweet.
The textures are balanced
just right,
so that nothing
loses its impact.
He changes up temperatures and
spices left and right,
always altering the rhythm
without disrupting the
overall flow of the meal!
Making each dish complete
in and of itself
is just so difficult.
The No. 1 Seat...
is something else!
[TSUKASA] Soma Yukihira...
And I take it, you must
be Megumi Tadokoro.
Is it, like, too cold in here?
I can turn it up!
If the air's blowing too hard,
just let me know, okay?
Are the chairs comfy enough
enough for you guys?
You don't find the lighting
too bright, do you?!
Look, going on and on and
hovering is ruining our dinner.
You're making everyone
uncomfortable.
[TSUKASA] (waahhh!)
Isn't that right,
my sweet Megumi?
Uh, um, well, maybe just a
little bit weirded out.
[TSUKASA] Oh, god!
So then, what should I do
when I come to the table?!
Like I always tell you,
just stand there and look
really pleased with yourself.
Your ability to determine the
strength of each ingredient
is second-to-none.
You've got a great eye.
But I want to taste something
that has more of your passion
involved on the plate,
something that
screams your name.
Oh, no.
My cooking must never be
so self-conscious.
[MEGUMI] Huh?
[TSUKASA] My job is to
completely remove myself
from the dish.
I devote myself solely to the
quality of the ingredients,
and to do my best
in elevating them.
And yet, conversely, that
process ties exactly into how I
always choose to express myself.
That is the essence of
Eishi Tsukasa's cooking.
Now then,
I hope you enjoy your meal.
And before anyone of us knew it,
this is what the gourmands
out there started to call him:
He who stays true to the finest
of ingredients, presenting them
in all their pride and glory:
"Der Weisse Ritter der Tafel."
[laughter] Pretty cool, huh?
The first time I saw tha
in a magazine, I busted
my gut laughing! [laughter]
[SOMA] Hey, Megumi,
did you happen to notice that?
As timid as that guy seems,
he never once asked us,
"How does it taste?"
That wasn't his concern.
He has absolute pride and
confidence in his ability to
handle the ingredients.
He's different from any chef
I've ever met.
That's what makes the
No. 1 Seat on the Ten.
[HISAKO] Ms Erina,
the Lunar Feast will be ending
pretty soon, right?
It will.
He didn't come... yet again.
[YOUNG ERINA] Um, Mr Saiba?
[JOICHIRO] Hmm?
I want to become an amazing cook
just like you when
I grow up to be big.
And then one day,
when I do that,
would please come and eat
what I've made for you?
Yeah, well, tell you what:
Once you've become a famous,
talented chef,
I will take you up on that.
And I will look forward
to that day,
when I get to try
your masterpiece.
It's all been for the
day he arrives.
[doors opening]
[BOTH] (hmmm?)
Everyone with reservations
is already accounted for.
I'll go take a look.
It couldn't be!
Um, excuse me, sir?
We're by reservation only, so-
[shocked gasp]
Hisako?!
[AZAMI]
It's been quite a while, Erina.
[ERINA] Father?
[contented sigh]
That really was some truly
amazing food tonight.
I was blown away by all of it!
I never thought a cooking world
like that ever existed.
Um, Soma?
Oh, yeah, the Mountain Area is
a force to be reckoned with!
He's totally on fire...
[SOMA] I wanna walk around
and see some more!
[MEGUMI] But we don't have
any Pine Tree tickets.
Oh, hey, there's always
Erina's place.
[MEGUMI] Uh, but...
It'll be fine.
On the first day
of the festival:
I got some black pepper rice
cakes. Go on, have one!
I'm not eating
any of your trash!
It's a good thing
I got on her good side.
I think you kind of forced that
peppered rice cake on her.
[HISAKO]
U-um, you can't do this!
Erina,
what is all this nonsense?
Your cooking is not meant for
the likes of these people.
[HISAKO] (frightened)
You should choose only those
involved in the business.
Otherwise,
your skills will weaken.
Excuse me! Do you have any idea
who you have the honor of
addressing right now, young man?
Who do you think you are?
I've seen this man somewhere
before, I believe. I think...
He's a Nakiri!
[KITA] (wha?) Impossible!
If I recall correctly,
you were driven out of
Totsuki years ago!
You're correct.
I am indeed Azami Nakiri.
And I'm Erina Nakiri's father.
[frightened shudder]
[HISAKO] Ms Erina's father...
Azami Nakiri!
I've only come across him
once in the school archives.
[HISAKO'S DAD] Hisako,
please listen to me.
You must ask no one
about Ms Erina's father.
Understand?
[YOUNG HISAKO] (ah-huh)
[HISAKO] He was essentially
erased from the Nakiri family.
What business does he have
with Ms Erina now?
Well, YOU talk big for someone
who was expelled before.
WE, on the other hand, have
legitimate dealings when
it comes to Totsuki.
Very true, dear sister!
So, when you insult
us like that,
you've managed to also show
contempt for Totsuki itself.
I have come to Totsuki
to fix it,
and guide it to its
proper form once again.
[BOTH] What was that again?!
[AZAMI] How many people
have you come across
who claim to work in the
culinary industry,
and can actually understand
what is truly delicious?
Only those with a sense of
dignity and sensibility,
and who have received
the proper education,
grasp the true worth
of great artistry.
This encapsulates fine dining.
Its value should be shared
with only a select few
of chosen worth.
Only then is it worth
being called "cuisine."
Or else it's not true
cooking at all; it is slop.
I doubt any who would mistake
a meal for fine cuisine
just because it uses
quality ingredients
would be able to understand
what I'm talking about.
You've got some damn nerve
saying that!
[ORIE] Thank you SO much for
sharing your thoughts with us.
But no matter what you say,
it will change nothing.
[NATSUME] Exactly! You no longer
have the right to make any
changes here at Totsuki!
But I have the bloodline,
now don't I?
And don't forget
the training as well.
Now, Erina...
It's been 10 years
since I began teaching you.
You started very young.
I'd like to see how far
you've come, daughter.
Um, but we can't!
We don't allow customers
in without a-
I think I see a table
open right over there.
No, that seat is for-
I'd like a menu, please.
Your father grows hungry.
I would like to
eat something now.
[ERINA] (shaky breath)
[HISAKO]
You all right, Ms Erina?
Um... I'm fine.
[SOMA] Hey, hey, Erina!
You got an open table? (chuckle)
Um, Soma, you came?
[laughing] Sorry for bargin'
in without a reservation,
but you think I could have
some of your eats?
I brought you a hujiao bing
to make up for it!
What's going on?
It feels like there's a lot
of tension in the room.
[SOMA] Hey, old man,
I didn't mean to intrude.
I take it you were just about
to order some grub.
Maybe I could, uh,
grab the seat and join ya?
If you don't mind?
Erina, why don't you go ahead
and seat your friend instead.
Soma Yukihira is here!
I've suddenly lost my appetite.
Hisako, who was that?
That man was Ms Erina's father.
[MEGUMI] (huh?)
What was with the
Man in Black there?
He should've stayed to eat.
Um, Erina, why are you shaking?
[AZAMI] I was just about to
come and pay you a visit.
I feel quite honored you chose
to come to me instead.
It's been a long time, Father.
Begone, ingrate!
You've no right to be
on these premises!
You were banished long ago!
And I believe I told you:
You are forbidden to use
the Nakiri name!
But it was I, her father,
who helped Erina develope
the "God Tongue"
she was blessed
with at birth.
You may try to drive me away,
but you cannot erase her
bloodline nor her education.
I cannot erase what has
already been done.
Entrusting Erina to you
was my greatest mistake.
We both have our mistakes
we must bear.
If I had remained, I would
never have let Totsuki
become what it is now:
an unsightly place filled with
nothing but mediocrity.
[exhausted sigh] Oh, Soma,
so this is where you've been!
What's the matter, Chef Rindo?
I was having a little snack
when I saw all these black
cars go racing by,
so I chased them here to
see what was going on.
We don't really know what's
going on out here either.
It looks like Erina's father
suddenly showed up
out of the blue.
[RINDO] (oh!)
At this school, cooking is
the only thing that will
ever matter.
So long as one has the skill,
they are free to advance.
That is the heaert of
the Totsuki's legacy.
It's disgusting.
Thinking that some lowbrow
student would be able
to cultivate the fine art of
true cuisine is the height of
fallacy, even for you.
[SENZAEMON]
You're a fool; you know nothing!
It is the very talent and drive
of these so called
"lowbrow" young chefs
that will decide the
future of Totsuki!
You can whine all you want,
but it will not change anything!
[AZAMI]
Totsuki Council of Ten....
They are bestowed with
as much power, if not more,
as the school director.
Is that true, old man?
For example, if a majority of
the members enact a policy,
then the school must adopt it,
no matter what.
So, Soma Yukihira, which one
would you like to choose?
What? I don't have any idea
what's going on right now.
Oh, whoops.
I thought maybe you would've
gotten on board instantly.
Wha?
[shocked grunt]
What? No! This is...
A majority of the
Council of Ten have voted
that a change is in order.
They have endorsed ME as
the new school director,
meaning you need to
step aside now.
A new wave in coming in
to take over.
And the mere thought
of riding it
makes my heart pound!
The most powerful organization
at Totsuki has managed to
stage a secret coup?!
[AZAMI] By this time tomorrow,
everything will be settled.
We will be the pride of Japan,
a kingdom of cuisine.
And I...
shall be its new king!
[music playing]