Did you say Joichiro Saiba?
'Cause, uh, that's my father.
[raining]
Chef Saiba and Soma are...
...father and son?
[AZAMI] Chef Saiba...
I'll finish this revolution,
and change the world,
without fail.
In order to save us
from any further sacrifices,
like yourself.
[music playing]
[on TV]
Do I really have to?
I keep telling you I'm not
the type who does well
speaking in front of crowds.
Oh, man-up and just start
talking, Tsukasa.
[sigh] If only Isshiki and
Erina were here too...
So, how many minutes until
we have to go live?
We're already live, Tsukasa.
[TSUKASA] (waahhh!)
(monotone)
Um, hello and welcome.
I am Eishi Tsukasa from Central.
I'm here today to tell you
about the big event
that marks the end of the 2nd
semester for the first years.
In other words, we'll be
discussing the Advancement Exam.
Last year, more than half of
the students failed and
left the academy.
It was an incredibly
challenging exam.
But things are different now!
Thanks to Director Azami,
you've all been freed
from the unnecessary
traditions of failure.
From now on, if you simply
follow the methods that we've
taught during your classes
it should be possible for
you to clear the exam.
You no longer need to
feel threatened or held back
by the archaic ways
of the old system.
If you agree to abide by
Central's exact methods,
you can all become
first-rate chefs.
However...
this exam shall also make clear
what will become of
certain rebels,
those who choose not to follow
Director Azami's new order.
Well then, that's about all
I have to say for right now.
Wow, my nerves are a wreck.
Next time Rindo or Nene
should do it instead.
[RYOKO] Not happening.
[NENE] Go to Hell.
Huh?
The Advancement Exam already?
It feels early since we're
only in the 2nd semester,
but if we wanna be second years,
we'll just have to nail it.
Oh god...
Hey what's up with you guys,
why the long faces?
Come on, were you even
listening just now?!
Central is aiming to
get rid of us rebels
by making sure that we fail
in the upcoming exams.
That announcement was just like
giving us a death sentence.
It's a warning that anyone who
doesn't follow Azami Nakiri
will be promptly eliminated.
I'm so sorry, Mom,
and everyone else
back at the port.
You worked so hard to send me
to Tokyo, but unfortunately...
I guess I'll send them
the news in the mail.
I'm having flashbacks of that
hellish training camp...
[GUYS]
Hellish training camp...
[YUKI] ...the Stagiarie where
we all worked so hard...
[GUYS] Stagiarie...
[SHUN] What's gotten into them?
[RYOKO] They're falling into
a depression spiral.
[YUKI] The Lunar Festival where
we all worked together...
[HISAKO] Just take a
deep breath, everyone.
[GUYS] Lunar Festival...
[MEGUMI] I suppose we all should
write letters back home.
[owl hooting]
[TSUKASA] This exam shall
also make clear what will
become of certain rebels,
those who choose not follow
Director Azami's new order.
[knock on door]
[SOMA] Who's there?
Door's open!
[SOMA] Erina?
What's wrong?
You need somethin'?
Um, I just...
I'm here to speak with you
about your battle
against Tsukasa.
I want to make it absolutely
clear you have no right
to complain
that I didn't choose
your dish over his!
It's your fault for being
reckless enough to
accept his challenge!
I won't deny there was a clear
difference in skill between us.
Huh?! What?! Oh...
So as long as
you understand that!
[SOMA] Is that all you wanted?
[ERINA] Uh, um, no!
What I really wanted to
talk with you about is, uh...
All right then, whatever.
Have yourself a seat.
[ERINA] Truth be told, until I
reached a certain point...
It's just...
Well, I'm quite certain that,
that I never held a passion
for cooking up until one
particular day.
As someone who possessed
the God Tongue,
I spent nearly every day
tasting numerous dishes.
But I never really enjoyed it.
I simply spent those days
disappointed by every bite.
That was when I met Chef Saiba.
[ERINA] It wasn't very long
after Alice had left me for
Northern Europe.
On that day,
my taste testing session
had been suddenly cancelled.
There were no guests
in the mansion,
so I remember that
it was very quiet.
[smells enticing aroma]
What's that?
Grandfather?
Who's that man with him?
It smells so delicious.
Erina?!
What's going on,
Master Senzaemon?
You know this isn't
what we agreed to.
I only came 'cuz you told me
that you'd cleared
everybody outta here.
I'm sorry,
my tasting job for today
was cancelled due to problems
on the other end.
I see.
Well, this man behind me
is an old dear friend of mine,
Erina.
This is supposed to be a private
meal between him and me.
I'm sorry.
I apologize.
I'll leave you alone,
Grandfather.
Your name was Erina, right?
I see, you must be Azami's kid.
If you would like,
stick around and have a bite.
The dining table feels
a little empty when it's
only set for two.
All right, eat up.
[happy surpirse]
From deep in my heart,
I feel a warmth welling up...
This is totally different from
any meal I've had before!
What fun!
[YOUNG ERINA] Um...
If you'd be so kind, sir,
may I please have your name?
It's Saiba.
[ERINA] That was the first day
that I thought cooking
could be wonderful.
But...
[AZAMI] An ill-prepared dish
is unforgivable.
Anything that does not
meet my approval is...
Filth!
Garbage!
Trash!
About 6 months after that,
I began learning from my father.
I still remember how moved I was
after I ate Chef Saiba's
food that day.
However, I understand the
benefits that my father seeks,
the ideal that he speaks of.
Our society is full of
uninspired and tasteless dishes
that pass for "food".
I've experienced the reality
of that for as long as
I can remember.
It's how I was raised.
But I feel I've lost something,
like the sense of what "cooking"
as an art really means.
I'm no longer able to recognize
the fundamentals, not anymore.
It's left me confused.
Uh-huh...
Uh, I'm sorry!
I came here without thinking it
all the way through.
I realize that dumping this
on you is inappropriate.
Please excuse me.
Just hold on a second.
I think having another taste
will set you straight.
So, I'll cook something up...
Yukihira style!
Right here and now!
Hang tight, Mistress Nakiri.
[HISAKO] Ms Erina!
Has anybody seen Ms Erina?!
Ms Erina?! Ms Erina!
[HISAKO] Ms Erinaaaa!!
[YUKI]
What's wrong, Miss Secretary?
Don't call me that!
I can't seem to find
Ms Erina anywhere!
Maybe she's just in the
bathroom or something?
I looked but she wasn't there!
She might have been taken away
by Azami again!
I lost track of her
only for a second,
and yet she still fell
into his clutches!
I'm a failure!
[HISAKO] I should have hired
a body double
[MEGUMI (hears something)
[MEGUMI] It sounds like she's
hanging out in Soma's room.
[HISAKO] or even made a fake
stand-in with my 3D printer!
[ALL] (huh?!)
[ERINA] You're going to make
a Yukihira dish for me to
taste right now?
What do you expect to
accomplish with that?!
Chef Saiba's dish was a
masterpiece of perfection
that your measly skills could
never ever, ever dream
of replicating!
Oh, so you're finally dropping
the meek, little girl persona
you had going.
Anyway, my dad always made sure
to teach me about his style
of cooking.
If I give you a taste of
one of his recipes,
it might help jog your
memory or something.
Well, then, what dish are
you planning to make?
Tempura bowl.
Tempura?
[SOMA] Just sit back.
I'll give you a taste of
something that will
knock you off your feet.
[mischievous chuckle]
Ah! I just know he's makin'
that face he makes
before he makes something
gross!
[SOMA] (evil little laugh)
[RYOKO] Just what kind of
tempura do you think he's
going to make for her?!
[ZENJI] But Erina has
the God Tongue!
With such refined taste buds, if
she eats Soma's weird cooking...
[AOKI]
Yeah, she's totally hozed.
[HISAKO] [scream of horror!]
It's gonna be okay!
It's not what it sounds like.
Soma is cooking because he
wants to convey something
important to Erina!
[BOTH] Megumi...
[RYOKO] She suffers from his
weird cooking the most.
[YUKI] Even if she's the one
saying otherwise...
[BOTH] ...it doesn't
sound very convincing.
[HISAKO] Yukihira...
[MEGUMI] Soma...
[SOMA]
The bonito flakes are boiling.
The batter is ready, too.
Lucky for you, I left some rice
already soaking in water.
Just wait, I'll serve you up a
super delicious bowl of tempura!
Soma Yukihira...
You had the same expression
on that day, too.
The day that Eishi Tsukasa,
First Seat of the Council,
challenged you.
Even though you were trying to
climb an insurmountable wall,
your expression only showed
how much fun you were
having cooking.
I was capable of the same
expression when I was young,
but now... now...
[MAN] Ms Erina, you have a
responsibility to uphold
the Nakiri family.
[WOMAN] You must act in
consideration of the family
as a whole,
rather than just yourself.
[MAN 2] She has the God Tongue.
We should start
buttering her up.
[MAN 3]
(Ohhh) You know that's right.
[ALICE] Guess what, Erina!
Someday, I'm going to be
the best chef
that ever went to
Totsuki Academy!
If I put my heart into
perfecting dishes,
I just know cooking
will be super fun!
But I won't go easy on you just
because you're my cousin!
I'm gonna do my best!
Um, okay. Sounds good.
[ERINA] I'm sorry, Alice.
But I just don't think any
aspect of the cooking process
is fun at all.
[SOMA] You've got doom and gloom
all over your face again.
You're usually such a priss,
but occasionally I do catch you
looking vulnerable.
Um, what's that mean?
[SOMA] I need you to stay sharp.
I mean, after all...
I'm about to get my revenge
for that first day we met.
So, I'm chomping at
the bit over here.
Disgusting!
[SOMA] Just you wait,
Erina Nakiri!
I'm gonna make that
mouth of yours
say my food is delicious!
[SOMA] And today is the day
I hear it straight
from your mouth:
That you think
my food is delicious!
Order up, Erina!
Your confidence knows no bounds.
Exactly what kind of dish do you
expect will win me over?
[heh] That's easy.
The one and only Yukihira-style,
Chicken Egg Tempura Bowl!
"Chicken egg tempura" bowl?
I've never heard of that.
[crunch]
[ERINA] This egg!
The whites are firm enough
to hold its shape,
but the yolk is still
incredibly runny!
It's perfectly soft boiled!
[huh?] Does that mean
he used a raw egg?
How the heck did he fry that?!
I don't think it would be
possible for him
to just take a raw egg
and put it in oil.
And you couldn't cover
a raw egg in batter.
That means he put it in
with the shell intact!
Dude, wouldn't that mean
you'd eat the shell, too?
Wait, did he just put a
soft-boiled egg in the
batter and fry it?
No, if he did that it would
get thoroughly cooked by
the heat of the oil.
How is this dish
even possible?!
It's kinda mysterious.
Bet it's got you real curious.
Your cocky attitude is
annoying as ever!
If you want the secret,
it's right here.
[ERINA] You put the eggs
in the freezer?!
This tempura was made
from frozen eggs
that were covered in batter
and then fried.
It's what makes
this dish special.
You remove the shell
from the frozen egg,
cover it in tempura batter,
and quickly put it in the fryer.
Cover the freshly cooked rice
with a healthy dose of sauce,
and let the egg sit on top, next
to some deep-fried shiso leaves.
Then, finish it off with
a drizzle of sauce.
[ERINA] I see.
But such creative cooking
is not nearly enough
to try and win me over, is it?
Dishes with egg as the main draw
are always simple,
which precisely means,
the chef's skill and
quality of the ingredients
have a direct impact
on the end result.
You offered this dish
to my God Tongue,
so it's too late
for any regrets.
Oh, dude, Erina-poo's
actually going to eat it!
Yeah, but whether it'll pass her
judgment is the question.
[RYOKO] Wait...
[MEGUMI] What's the matter?
I remember seeing something
the other day.
I caught a glimpse of Soma
doing some shopping.
He bought up a whole bunch of
cheap eggs at 106 a pack!
[SOMA] (cackling)
He bought eggs that
were on sale?!
This is bad! Ms Erina was
raised in a household
that made it a point to partake
in only the best and most
carefully selected ingredients!
There's no telling what a bunch
of cheap ingredients will do.
It could prove dangerous when
in contact with her body.
[ALL] (gasps of surprise)
[dramtic music building]
Erina-poo! No, don't eat it!
[musical crescendo!]
[ERINA] The eggs that you
used in this dish...
I could tell from one bite
they were not from a
high-class silkie,
or even one of
the famous brands.
They're completely generic
and low level.
Far from what is
high-class cuisine.
And yet...
Peep!
Peep! Peep!
[lots of peeps]
[moans of delight]
[ERINA] How?
[peeping continues]
How can it be so deep?
Such a rich and
complex flavor...
[ecstatic moan] ...is coming to
life right before me!
[chuckle] When you put eggs
in the freezer,
they undergo multiple changes,
and that comes with one
major benefit, which is:
the flavor of the yolk will then
start to become stronger
and more concentrated.
The flavor of the yolk
will become stronger?!
And by freezing chicken eggs,
the protein inside becomes hard
and thick like a jelly.
Thanks to that, it has
an overall creamier and
more doughy texture.
And in particular, the taste
of the yolk becomes deeper
and more impactful.
The whole point of the dish
is using frozen eggs to capture
that delicious flavor.
I covered the dish with the
Yukihira special-blend of super
umami sweet and sour sauce.
It stays nice and rich with
bonito dashi blended with
soy sauce and mirin.
And of course, it goes perfectly
with the rice, too!
Now if I had used high-end eggs
that are already rich in flavor,
it would ruin the balance
of the whole dish.
[gasp]
Wait, is that why you...
Eggsactly, the unique texture
and taste of frozen eggs,
Plus the flavor of
the special sauce.
In order to bring them together,
the best choice is using
a totally ordinary egg.
I get it!
That means he chose
those discount eggs
for this specific purpose!
Soma is just the best!
If I think back to it now,
the theme ingredient you chose
on that day was also eggs,
right?
To bring an end to
our long-time rivalry,
there's nothin' more suitable
than this, don't you think?
[ERINA] How?
[SOMA] (hmm?)
[ERINA] How do you come up
with dishes like this?!
When it comes to eggs,
the fresher the better
is common sense!
And isn't it natural for
chefs to strive for
the rarest and highest-quality
ingredients possible?
But despite all of that,
how can you just-
[SOMA] Don't you think
this way is more fun?
This is my personal and
humble opinion, but...
People who believe there's
only one way to do things
will never be able to
reach greater heights in
whatever they're doing.
And on top of all that...
[YOUNG ERINA] Um, tell me,
how did you come up with
the ideas for your
wonderful dishes?
All of them were so eccentric
and new to me,
but felt so refined
at the same time.
Did you know from the start
that they would turn out
so perfectly delicious?
[JOICHIRO] I had no clue.
[ERINA] What?
Whenever I try a
new idea for a dish,
I'm only half certain
and gamble the rest.
And as a matter of fact,
I was using your gramps to
test a number of new ideas.
But why would you risk so much?
Well, that is simple.
[BOTH] If I already knew
the dish's outcome,
where would the fun be in that?
Oh, that's right.
I just remembered.
[scarfing]
This...
[happy eating]
This is the kind of cooking
that I wanted to do!
I finally remembered....
[sigh of relief]
[AZAMI] Listen up, Erina.
Only the food of
which I approve,
of which Central creates,
is true cuisine!
[ERINA] No...
[AZAMI] I will eliminate
all slop from this school
and raise every student
to be a faithful soldier
dispensing culinary greatness.
That's the only way to
make Totsuki stronger.
[ERINA] No!
[AZAMI] The "true cuisine"
of which I herald
is the absolute justice
of this world.
Not true!
Father, both chefs
and the food they create,
surely must desire
their freedom!
So, what'd ya think?
Of the Yukihira-style
special dish?
Come on! I'd like to hear each
and every one of your thoughts
on my awesome dish, Erina.
Delicious, right?
Absolutely divine? Right?!
I've made up my mind.
[SOMA] Huh?
Okay, Soma, I need you to do
exactly what I'm
about to tell you.
[SOMA] Huh?
At 7 AM tomorrow, I'd like you
to go and gather everyone in the
dorm outside by the entrance.
Uh, um, yeah,
sure I can do that.
But what about my dish?
Great, I'm counting on you.
I have preparations that
I must go make.
Wait! What about my dish?!
Oh, and one more thing.
I need you to go
and tell Megumi...
Tell her to shred up the letter
she wrote to her family.
She's not going to be needing
to say that anymore.
Huh?
[ALL] (confused)
What exactly happened
in the end there?
[AOKI] It's freezing out here!
[others shivering]
[SHUN] Well, it's already winter
according to the calendar.
Man, I guess this will be
one of the last times we
enjoy the view out here.
We're done once
the Advancement Exam hits, bro.
I wonder what Erina is planning
for all of us to do while
we're out here?
Well, she didn't explain
anything to me, that's for sure.
Ms Erina...
Oh, Erina-poo?
[ERINA] Ahem...
[over bullhorn]
Greetings,
residents of Kyokusei Dorm.
[AOKI] What's going on?
Well!
From what I can see from here,
you've all still got pitiful
looks on your faces.
[YUKI] Huh?
[ERINA] At this point,
the end result is obvious,
even without the
Advancement Exam.
Perhaps it would be easier
if you all just left the
academy right now.
What? Did you get us all
out here just to talk
a bunch of smack?!
We all wanna stay!
And we want to continue cooking
our own style of food!
But we're not allowed, and you
don't have to scold us about it!
Only a brief time has passed
since I came to stay with you.
And while I have been
staying here at the dorm,
I have had many...
let's just say, opportunities
to sample all of your dishes.
The flavors were often erratic,
and sometimes a complete mess.
I've lost count of the number
of times I've delivered
my criticism.
However, I can say
with certainty,
every dish tasted of freedom.
Now look! You'll never live up
to your true potential
if you continue staying
down in the dumps
and just allow yourself
to flunk out now!
It's pathetic! Are you going
to roll over like this?!
But even if we tried
to do it our way,
how are we supposed to get
through the exam?!
[ERINA] It's not a question
of getting through it!
You must simply forge your
own path with your cooking!
[ZENJI] Woah!
She's starting to sound
a lot like Soma.
Ms Erina...
[ERINA] I started to
think more seriously...
About what I really want...
What I want to accomplish
as a person.
[ERINA] If all of you have
the will to fight on
and wish to continue
staying here...
I shall use my God Tongue,
and support you in
realizing your potential!
Those of you without the will to
fight should leave right now.
I will only face this exam with
those of you who have the
strength needed to forge on.
Now! If you believe you are
truly honorable chefs,
[music begins]
then step up to the plate
and follow my lead!