Hey! Don't change that channel!
You don't wanna miss
a second of this one!
Koutaro's back at school,
and in a girl's uniform, too!
It looks good, but a
shrine maiden's outfit
might look better!
All teachers are looking
for diamonds in the rough,
and I Junichiro Kagami,
the Ultimate Otaku Teacher,
always find them first!
[FEMALE PLAYER A]
Look, it's Luce!
[MALE PLAYER A]
Huh. She's all alone this time.
[MALE PLAYER B]
Wait, what, you didn't hear?
[FEMALE PLAYER B] Remember that
event the other day?
She was competing
with her partner, First,
and they had some bet going on.
Anyway, he lost and the
admins erased his account.
[SUZUNE]
see you!
[KOUTARO]
Oh, hey you guys.
--Hi, Koutaro!
I, uh, suppose Mr. Kagami's
doing okay?
Yeah! Same old, same old.
You know, you could
always stop by the house
and see for yourself.
Or better yet,
come to school with us and
you can see him every day!
Maybe so. I think I'm ready.
Of course you are!
You've already got
lots of friends!
Yeah, don't worry!
We've got your back.
Well, see ya soon!
[KOUTARO gasps]
That accessory she's wearing.
[FEMALE STUDENT A]
Morning!
[MALE STUDENT A]
Good morning.
[FEMALE STUDENT B]
Hey, Kanan's here!
[MALE STUDENT B]
Ughhhh, she's so cute!
[FEMALE STUDENT C]
Yeah, it's ridiculous!
I'm totes jelly!
[MALE STUDENT C]
Be my girlfriend!
[MALE STUDENT D]
Hey, screw you! Get in line!
[KANAN giggles]
Another day in the life of
the cutest girl
in school! Goodness!
Whatever shall I do
with all of these fans?
[MALE STUDENT E]
Hey, look!
[MALE STUDENT F]
Who's that cute girl?
[MALE STUDENT B] I've never
seen her before, have you?
[MALE STUDENT H] Nah, but I
wanna get to know her!
[MALE STUDENT C] There's no way
the whole school missed her.
Not someone that cute.
Guess it's her first day.
[MALE STUDENT G]
Wonder which class she's in.
[KANAN gasps]
Huh?
Uh... Koutaro?
[KANAN chuckles]
Well, huh, a girl's uniform.
Not what I expected, but I
guess we'll see what happens!
[KOUTARO]
Here goes.
Uh... How's everybody
doing today?
Wait, what? Koutaro?
Oh, wow.
A girl's uniform, huh?
[KOUTARO sighs]
Oh.
I'm so glad you could
make it, Koutaro!
I, uh, put a lot of
thought into this.
I decided I didn't wanna be
dishonest about myself.
I had confidence in wearing
this, but was it a bad idea?
'Course not! Just give
people some time.
Actually, you look so good,
everyone's gonna
be jealous of you.
Hey, 'sup.
[gasps]
Hi, Seijuro!
Morning. You decided to show up.
Is it a little weird
that I'm wearing this?
No. Is it supposed to be?
I mean, that's what
you usually dress like,
far as anyone's seen.
Now, if you started dressing
like a dude all of a sudden,
that would be weird.
Uh, thank you, Seijuro.
Hmph.
Hey, am I crazy?
No, Seijuro just said
something nice.
[JUNICHIRO]
I heard Koutaro's here!
[KOUTARO]
Mr. Kagami!
Wow, glad you
could make it! Nice!
Knew you'd look
good in our uniform!
Thank you, but...
I wanted to say.
[MAKINA] Hey! I heard
Koutaro showed up today!
Is it true?
Oh wow, I'm so happy!
How mean! You should've told me!
I was so looking forward to
escorting you on your first day!
It was going to be
a big moment for us!
Oh. Sorry 'bout that.
Since when does
Makina give out hugs?
Oh, Options. What brings you all
the way down here? Kinda busy.
I heard we had an extra cute
new student, so I had to see.
Unfortunately, your uniform...
is against the rules.
[KOUTARO]
Uh...
It does suit you quite nicely.
[KOUTARO gasps]
[MAKINA]
But this is my job.
And I'm afraid the school
handbook is law here.
Gosh, you are
awfully cute, though.
Rules are rules, I guess.
Yeah, this must be a first.
[KOUTARO]
Uh...
Accepted!
--Huh?
I make the calls here,
and I say this is the
uniform you belong in.
Now good day!
Thanks, Options.
That's a big help.
[KOYOMI]
Hm?
If Koutaro's comfortable here,
we won't have to worry
about any more truancy.
[KOYOMI] Please, you needn't
act as if I've performed
some great favor.
I only did what I thought
was most amusing.
[chuckles]
[school bells ring]
[KOUTARO]
Oh, Mr. Kagami!
Wait a sec!
[KOUTARO gasps]
Hey, there he is!
So cute!
I can't believe that
you're really a guy!
Uh, yeah. I really am.
[MALE STUDENT E]
Move it man, lemme see!
[MALE STUDENT F]
Wait your turn!
[MALE STUDENT G] I think
we've got a new number one.
Sorry, ladies!
Please you guys, stop it.
I'm embarrassed.
Oh wow, my blood's boiling now!
Koutaro needs a
maid uniform next!
Welcome home, Master,
I'm sorry to keep you waiting!
You just have to come work
with me after school!
Everyone's gonna go nuts,
you'll be a star in
no time, I guarantee it!
Oh, yeah?
I'll come to see you!
Not if I do first!
Well, somebody sure is popular!
Not good. Not good at all.
If this keeps up, my position as
"undisputed cutest girl
on campus" will be in jeopardy!
I don't know about the
"undisputed" part.
[KANAN]
Ugh.
I overheard some people.
They said you were way cooler
and more mysterious
when you didn't talk.
[squeaks]
And not my words here, but also
they said you were old news.
I am so not old news.
But no biggie. Popularity
isn't everything, after all.
Now be nice.
I... have to do
something drastic.
[MALE CLASSMATE 17D] So, you
have a favorite type of food?
What kind of music
are you into?
[KANAN]
Ow!
[MALE CLASSMATES]
Huh?
Oh, no. I hurt my tushy!
[KANAN] Now stop paying
attention to Koutaro
and come help me up, you doofs!
Look at how cute I am! Heh!
[MALE CLASSMATE 17D]
Hey, uh, you maybe wanna
do something this Sunday?
I know this place.
[KANAN]
Rejected?
No, no, that can't be right!
They must not have heard me.
So much for subtlety!
Hm. Here goes!
Get a load of this, boys!
[MALE CLASSMATES gasp]
Oh, no!
[KANAN]
Bam!
[MALE CLASSMATE E]
Okay...
[KANAN]
You guys are cold!
What's your deal?
How 'bout this one?
[KANAN]
Bleh!
[MALE CLASSMATE D]
What is wrong with her?
[MALE CLASSMATE E]
I dunno, but don't look.
Suddenly, all of my contempt
is turning into pity.
I think I liked things better
when you two were friends.
[KANAN]
All right, you heartless swines.
[KANAN giggles]
Let's see you ignore this!
It looks like she's about
to really hurt herself,
should we do something,
you guys?
No way! Not our problem!
[KANAN]
Heh! I'll make you love me!
--Let's calm down!
--[gasp]
Kanan, no!
[yells]
[gasps]
[KANAN, KOUTORO grunt]
Whatever it is you're doing,
please stop, okay?
How, dare you!
I don't need sympathy
from my rival!
Huh?
You shouldn't be associating
with someone like me!
I'm nothing but
yesterday's garbage
in the world of
cute girl rankings!
I don't know what that means,
but you're perfectly cute to me!
Huh?
I forgot to tell you,
but that new accessory you
got in Uroboros is great.
You crafted it yourself,
didn't you?
I'd never seen anything like it,
and you know me,
I play all the time!
The point is it's not just
cute, but really smart, too.
Are you teasing me?
No, I mean, I never thought
to use a glitched item
in a vanity slot like that
and then use a crafting
class to edit the colors!
Players are always bragging
about their end-game loot,
but your item is way cooler
than any of that stuff.
You... really think so?
I used to think I'd mastered
the art of cuteness,
but you've shown me
I have a lot to learn!
Please, train me!
And you sure you're
not making fun of me?
[sighs, grunts]
Fine, I'll be your teacher!
And since you're
"The Ironclad Nun,"
you can call me "big sister"
from now on, okay?
Sure! Whatever you say!
I feel like Kanan is having some
sort of an identity crisis.
It's better than
hurting herself.
[KANAN] First, why don't you
show me what kind of stuff
you're into and we'll
take it from there.
[KOUTARO]
Okay!
If you see something
you think is cute,
then take a picture, okay?
Should be simple.
[KOUTARO]
I'll give it my best!
Okay, then we'll meet up at
the park an hour from now.
You ready?
--Let's go!
--Go!
[KOUTARO]
What's cute?
I need something good.
[KOUTARO]
Cute stuff.
[gasps]
[KOUTARO]
You're cute!
[cat meows]
Aw, it ran.
[gasps]
[KOUTARO]
I love it!
Find anything?
Send it over to my phone.
What do think about this one?
That's cute!
Okay, this one I really love.
It's a little offbeat so
promise you won't laugh?
Come on, just show me!
[KOUTARO]
This!
[KANAN]
A shrine maiden?
Uh-huh!
[gasps]
I love it!
[KOUTARO]
Ever since I was little,
I thought shrine maiden
outfits were adorable.
And look! the poster
says Shinmei Shrine
wants a part-time maiden to help
out at their summer festival!
So... let's do it!
We'll both be so cute!
Wait. We? I don't know.
C'mon! I'm too
shy to do it alone,
but if I have my big sister
with me, I know I'll be fine!
Hold on, the school
rules are really clear
about having a part time job.
There's no way Makina
will let this pass. Sorry.
Yeah? I had no idea.
Aw. That ruins it all.
And I was getting
so excited too.
Wow, speak of the devil.
[gasps]
Uh, ah...
Hey there, you two!
Go ahead and ask her.
[gasps]
Uh...
What's going on, Koutaro?
[KOUTARO whimpers]
You can tell me.
[giggles]
I have a favor to ask!
[MAKINA]
Uh.
I know we can't
have part-time jobs,
but can I be a shrine maiden,
just for a day?
A shrine maiden. For a day?
[KANAN]
So that's the story.
It means a lot!
Please let us do it.
[KOUTARO]
We're begging you!
I think it's great that you
and Koutaro want to go out
and be a part of something,
so I'd like to help support that
however I can. But any
way you look at it,
part-time jobs are
against the rules.
I'm afraid there's no
loophole on that one.
Can't you make a
one-time exception?
No, I have a job to do.
I can't pick and choose
with this sort of--
[gasps]
[whimpers]
[MAKINA]
I can't!
Well, I mean.
[whimpers]
[grunts]
Please, Miss Momozono!
Ah, fine! Fine!
Just this once!
Really?! Wow! Oh my gosh,
you're the best ever!
[KANAN] That cuteness...
is a dangerous weapon.
[CROWD chatters]
[KOUTARO]
Whoa!
Look, guys! They're so cute!
[giggles]
No offense, but why
did you come?
[MAKINA]
Hmph. Isn't it obvious?
I'm here to keep an eye on you.
Cause any trouble and the
part-time shrine maiden thing
is called off immediately!
[giggles] Oh my gosh, this is
like a dream come true!
Thank you so much!
By the way, did you happen to
let our dear otaku teacher
know about this?
Oh. No, should I
have said something?
Absolutely not. He'd turn
this into another one of
his lessons, when we're
totally fine on our own.
[MAKINA] Also, I don't want him
to see me dressed like this.
[MAKINA mocking]
Oh yeah, I get it!
you must work at the
temple of the twin tails!
[laughing]
[MAKINA] He might even give
me some awful new nickname.
[gasps]
Are you done changing
and ready to go?
Uh-huh!
[BOTH giggle]
[giggles]
[sighs]
[grunts]
[CROWD murmurs]
[GIRL] Mommy, I want
a good luck thing!
[MOTHER]
Okay!
[GIRL]
This one, this one!
[MOTHER]
One of those, please.
Sure thing, thank you!
We appreciate your business!
Come again soon!
[giggles]
Kanan, that's not what
you're supposed to say.
[KANAN]
Hm?
This isn't some random shop
at a mall, it's a shrine,
so you say, "Thank you
for the offering."
How would I know that?
[KOUTARO] Yes, is this
the one you wanted?
[VISITOR A]
Actually, these two.
[VISITOR B]
All three of these.
[VISITOR C]
I'll take all you've got!
[growls]
[KANAN] I guess upstaging
me at school isn't enough,
you adorable little jerk!
How shameless can you get!
But that's all right.
I won't be petty.
I'm her "big sister" now.
That's better than number one.
That's, like, the only one.
I have to set a good example
for my cuteness understudy!
I bet Makina is taking
this hard, though.
She's pretty snooty.
She probably thought
she was hot stuff.
It's funny. Did you
notice the crowd is a lot
thinner in front the two of us?
Oh, that doesn't matter.
This isn't a popularity contest.
We're here to support Koutaro.
[gasps] How is she being
so mature about this?
Stop making me look petty,
you little snoot!
[VISITOR D]
T-This one, please.
Welcome home, master.
I'll go get your French fries.
I thought so. She's totally
losing it over there.
[CROWD chatters]
[KOUTARO] I'm in need
of some sisterly advice.
Yeah? Is something wrong?
[KOUTARO] Um... I need to
go to the little girl's--
What's going on, guys?
Well, uh, we're having a bit of
a potty time logistical issue.
The boy's room is pretty
much out of the question
with a shrine maiden outfit on,
but Koutaro's still shy about
using the girl's room without
someone else to tag along.
That was bound to come
up sooner or later.
Go ahead and help him, Kanan.
I can handle things
here by myself.
Thanks, sorry 'bout this.
[KANAN]
All right, off we go!
[KOUTARO]
Sorry again!
It's fine.
Okay, all alone.
There's nothing to
freak out about.
I'm sure I'll manage somehow.
Can't be worse than
being a maid, after all.
[gasps]
Oh, this is the last
thing I need right now.
If it's so important, then go
buy it yourself, Suzune.
I told you, it needs
to be a gift from you,
or it won't be special and
won't even work right!
He's coming this way.
Oh yeah, I get it, you must work
at the temple of the twin tails!
[MAKINA]
But I can't abandon my post!
I have a responsibility!
I, uh, need a
lucky charm please.
Don't really care
which one, I guess.
Huh?
[MAKINA]
Whatever you please, sir.
Uh yeah, this one, then.
Hey, hold on.
[MAKINA grunts]
Is there something
going on here?
It's weird. I feel like
I know her. Maybe...
[MAKINA giggles]
Surely you are mistaken, sir,
for I have nary once gazed upon
your countenance, I assure you.
[chuckles]
[gasps]
All right. If you say so,
then it must be my mistake!
Here.
[MAKINA] Your patronage is
much appreciated, good sir.
[sighs] I can't believe
that plan actually worked.
[KANAN gasps]
Hi Mr. Kagami!
[gasps]
I'm digging the costumes!
So? What's the occasion?
This isn't a cosplay
festival, is it?
They aren't costumes!
We're real shrine maidens,
or one day part-time
shrine maidens,
if you want to get
technical about it.
Uh-huh!
Wait. Did you check
with the school first?
I thought getting a job
was against the rules.
Yep! But believe or not,
Makina made a special
exception just this once!
Wow! So old twin-tails
isn't as inflexible as she
makes herself out to be!
Well, actually.
[phone rings]
[gasps]
What? A text?
[MAKINA]
If you tell him
I'm doing the shrine
maiden thing too. Death!
[gasps]
Mommy, that weird
lady is scaring me!
Actually Makina also
decided she wanted to--
[KOUTARO gasps]
[KANAN]
What's going on?
[yelps]
She decided she wanted
to go home and stay away
from us and our part time shrine
maiden job, yeah that's it!
[BOTH giggle]
[JUNICHIRO]
Uh...
[JUNICHIRO] Starting today,
I, DJ Professor K,
am gonna be kicking tunes
your way every lunch break.
Let's start with a
personal favorite,
from Magical Cannon Girl--
No way! Nuh-uh!
Turn that off, now!
[JUNICHIRO] Ah! No! Wait!
We're still on the air!
[MAKINA yells]
[STUDENTS scream]
[JUNICHIRO screams]
I am so sick of dealing
with your nonsense!
Are you trying to pick
a fight with me?
Nobody was using the room.
I thought the students
would get a kick out of it!
This is expensive equipment!
They are not your toys!
No fair!
So Koutaro gets to
wear a girl's uniform
and work a part-time job,
but when I want to
have a little fun,
"Oh no! That won't do at all!"
I thought you were learning
to be more flexible,
but I guess I was wrong!
[grunts]
Wait, is that?
Oh.
[JUNICHIRO]
I got it last night.
Suzune made me go
to the festival.
Can't really complain, though.
The miko who sold it
to me was real cute.
[gasps]
She was a little shy,
but she could teach you
a lot about manners!
[gasps]
What, did I hit
a nerve, or something?
I don't think I've ever
seen a face so red before.
[gasps]
[MAKINA]
Silence!
Come back here and take
your punishment like a man!
[school bells ring]
I hurt.
I think that girl
needs a new nickname.
"Twin Tailed Gorilla" maybe.
[KOUTARO]
Mr. Kagami!
Mr. Kagami, wait,
let's walk together!
Well, as long as
you don't attack me.
So, how are things?
They're good. I just
wanted to chat.
[video game music plays]
[JUNICHIRO laughs] It's not
that I have anything against
gaming online, but it's nice
to play something in the same
room with you for a change.
Uh-huh!
Nowadays, it feels like
most multiplayer games
are competitive, so we have
to go a little old school
to get the experience
I was hoping for.
But for a long time now, I knew
if we ever met in person,
this is the one that I
wanted to play with you.
Yeah?
So, what did you need to say?
The reason I finally decided
to go out and come to school
was because I wanted to
be with you in real life,
not just online.
That's all I needed to tell you.
Huh?
Is this?
Yeah, for you.
Huh?
But why?
[JUNICHIRO]
It was Suzune's idea.
She was, ah, proud of you
for gathering your courage
and coming to school,
so we wanted to show
some moral support.
Well, thanks to
both of you, then.
I don't know if I can live
up to my online reputation,
but I'll try my best to be a
good partner in school, too!
Good! Then I'll be
counting on you, partner.
Speaking of which,
eyes on the screen!
[KOUTARO]
Oh, sorry.
[JUNICHIRO] Actually, I'm not so
sure about that good luck charm.
They had a bunch of
part-timers working that day,
so it might not be legit.
[KOUTARO laughs]
[KOUTARO] This is Koutaro
Araki from class two-three.
If I had known school
was going to be this fun,
I would've come a lot sooner!
All's well that
ends well, I guess.
Next episode is about Kazuya.
Miss Momozono's little brother!
Remember him?
Anyway, another kid
beat him in a card game
and took a mythic rare
card from his collection!
Period eighteen,
"A Gamer's Pride"
"If you lose something playing,
you win it back playing."
Ha. Ha. That sounds like
Mr. Kagami, all right.