Hey! Don't change that channel!
You're gonna love
what's next. I guarantee it!
What do a juvenile delinquent
and a pop idol have in common?
They're both getting
put on my lesson plan!
All teachers are looking for
diamonds in the rough,
and I Junichiro Kagami,
the Ultimate Otaku Teacher,
always find them first!
[NARRATOR] Activating a
mysterious item left behind
by their father,
five half-siblings now
defend the earth from
the evil forces of Nemesis!
[NARRATOR]
They are...
[FAMILY RANGERS] Fraternal
Force Family Rangers!
[Family Rangers theme plays]
[JUNICHIRO]
Hey! What are you doing?
[SUZUNE] What does it
look like I'm doing?
I'm turning on
the 5th Queens Concert.
[JUNICHIRO] Yeah, but I was
watching Family Rangers.
[SUZUNE]
And now you're not!
That show's, like,
ten years old or something.
You can watch it on DVD.
This concert is live, so I can
only watch it right now!
But the Rangers
have a power and a force
that you've never seen before!
If it's a show
of force you want,
I'm more than happy to oblige.
Just let me get my bat.
No! I'll just stream it.
Man, would you
look at Komi-Ryu.
She's absolutely
amazing! And so cute!
[JUNICHIRO] The power did
not protect us today.
Ugh. Will you please
hurry up already?
[JUNICHIRO] Remind me
again, what are we doing
out here exactly,
and why do I have to do it?
Like I told you before,
there have been
a lot of reports of street
gangs popping up here.
And, given our positions
in the school system,
it's up to you and me
to prevent any kids
from getting mixed up in them.
I guess that makes sense,
but how exactly
are we supposed to keep them
from getting in trouble?
By talking to them of course.
If they're obviously supposed
to be in school right now,
then we just have
to convince them to go.
And that means everyone.
Even if they're not
from Icho Academy.
Sounds like
a pain in the butt.
All right, it's time
to see what you've got.
But what do I say?
Start off by asking their age
and where they go to school.
Let's see. Go and
talk to that girl first.
Well, what are you waiting for?
[JUNICHIRO sighs]
Uh, hey there.
Got a second?
Do you mind if I
ask how old you are?
And what school you go to?
Uuuh...
[MAKINA] You barely even tried!
Do I have to do everything?
Excuse us, but aren't
you a little young
to be hanging out on the street
in the middle of the day?
You should be in school.
Oh really?
Well you're one to talk!
I was given permission
to be out here.
I'm on patrol!
Wow, that was nice
of your school to let you
go outside into the real world.
You handling it okay?
You look a little scared.
[grunts]
But seeing as you asked,
I'm fifteen years old.
My name's Taki Komiya.
And here's my school.
[BOTH]
Huh?
[MAKINA]
What are you talking about?
This is just an arcade.
If you take everything
at face value.
--What?
--Think about it.
The only reason people
go to school every day
is 'cause it's the
only place they get to see
all their friends and
have fun with them.
And I already do that here,
so this is the only
school I need.
That is complete nonsense.
That is completely awesome!
What a great philosophy
to live by!
Finally, someone gets it!
You're supposed
to be on my side.
But she's right.
Going to school's about
more than getting book smarts!
I heard that on TV once.
Have you forgotten
why we're out here?
Oh man, is there
anything more lame
than watching a fight unfold
between two old people?
[MAKINA] Watch your mouth,
street rat! I'm only eighteen!
Worse than I thought.
Well. All right, I'm done
talking about this.
Don't you walk away from me!
Hey! What the--?
She's gone.
Everything okay in here?
No, that girl just
disappeared into thin air.
How about we split up for a bit
and you leave this one to me?
That way you can
go on patrol somewhere else.
--[MAKINA] Mmm. Sure.
--[JUNICHIRO] 'Kay.
But take this seriously, okay?
Like Avada Kedavra.
[JUNICHIRO] It's safe.
You can come down now.
Can't believe
you figured me out!
[chuckles]
[JUNICHIRO] Like I haven't seen
that in a million cartoons.
But actually seeing it in the
flesh was certainly a treat.
Pshaw! If you think
that was something,
you should meet my sister.
She's got way cooler moves
than I could ever pull off.
I'm sure.
Anyway, I need to really
get back to patrolling.
That sounds like fun!
Can I come?
I definitely know this city
better than you do.
I guess that's fine.
Sure, why not?
[JUNICHIRO] Ooh. I never
knew there was a road here.
Technically that's
because there isn't.
This is actually all part of
an abandoned factory.
I stopped going to school
when I was thirteen,
and I've spent most
of my time since then
just drifting around town.
So I know all the secrets
of this place
like the back of my hand.
Meanwhile I've lived
my entire life in this city,
but I never had a clue.
It's starting to feel like
the teacher's
becoming the student here.
In that case,
here's a few more life lessons.
Every day that seafood
market changes its display box,
which teaches which fish
are in season when.
You can learn about dressmaking
at the used clothes store.
And you can meet musicians from
all over the world at that club!
See what I'm talking about?
I really do think of
this whole town as my school.
It's taught me everything
I know about the world.
And I wouldn't have learned
half of this stuff
if I had been stuck
sitting in class each day
like a normal kid.
[JUNICHIRO]
Hmmm.
[TAKI]
Finally! Let's do this!
This is heavy!
I can't believe there's still
a Family Rangers claw game.
Yup, I was waiting
for my turn at it,
but I got sidetracked.
Cough-by you-cough.
So you like Family Rangers?
Well, uh,
don't be hatin', dude.
It's been on since
I was a kid. It's nostalgic.
The Family Rangers
are five half-siblings
born from different
mothers and given powers
by an artifact
from their father.
A controversial team dynamic
that had never been explored
in the Rangers'
past incarnations!
Because of that,
each episode's plot was able
to juxtapose complex themes,
such as peace on Earth
against peace within the home,
in ways that resonated
with viewers of all ages.
In fact, it is so insanely
popular that it still airs
in reruns to this day!
[gasps in awe]
[BOTH]
Morphenomenal!
All right, there's no way I'm
leaving without a prize today!
You think you have
enough tokens?
Absolutely.
These games may be tough,
but when I play, I play to win!
[JUNICHIRO]
That's the spirit!
Uh?
Hey, we've got
trouble brewing.
What are you talking about?
Don't look now,
but I'm pretty sure
one of those street gangs
just showed up.
I know you said
"don't look," but I'm gonna.
Shoot, you're right!
Follow me!
[TAKI] 'Kay. Our only hope
of getting out of here
is through this window.
[JUNICHIRO]
Uh, right!
Okay.
[JUNICHIRO, TAKI panting]
Listen. Those guys?
They're from
the new gang in town.
They beat up anybody
they come across!
But worse? It's filmed!
High def. To sell. Online.
It's evil!
[JUNICHIRO]
Mmm!
Aah!
Hold on, bro.
You chose the perfect
time to run by.
'Cause I'm short on cash.
[JUNICHIRO]
Eeeh! Oh, please no!
I don't want to be filmed
and sold on the internet!
What the hell are you
talkin' about, man?
Shut up and give me
your wallet!
I was just starting
to have fun, but you had to
come along and ruin everything.
Huh?
Family... Kick!
[JUNICHIRO]
Huh?!
[TAKI]
Ha!
Oh, man, the guys
from the arcade
have caught up to us! Aah!
Not in the face!
Wut?
[DELINQUENT 19A] Is everything
all right, Miss Taki?
I'm fine. I didn't even
break a sweat.
[DELINQUENT 19B] Heh. Where'd
this guy come from, anyway?
[TAKI] Who cares? He's just
some random loser.
[DELINQUENT 19A]
Yeah I see that,
so why did you run from us?
[TAKI] I just wanted
to have a little fun.
[JUNICHIRO]
Whaaat?!
You mean to tell me these guys
are friends of yours?
[TAKI]
Mhm!
When were you
planning on telling me?
I thought we were dead for sure!
You're fine!
You should have seen
the look on your face, though--
it was hilarious!
This's messed up.
It's time I come clean.
I'm actually the leader
of Black Oracle Neo,
and if there's
one thing I can't stand,
it's letting something fun
slip through my fingers.
Why don't you just admit it?
You had a good time.
Black Oracle Neo?
Worst street gang name ever.
Every one of us are misfits.
For one reason or another,
none of us fit in at
home or at school,
so we took to the streets
in hopes of finding
our own place in the world.
Every person deserves
a place where they belong.
If no one wants us around,
then we'll give that
to each other.
Guess that makes sense.
[TAKI] Junichiro,
you said you thought
my philosophy was awesome.
And honestly? I think
you're awesome, too!
So why don't you join us?
It'll be a lot of fun!
--[JUNICHIRO] I re--
--[TAKI] I refuse!
[gasps]
That's what you were
gonna say, right?
After hanging out
with you today,
I can tell you're not the type.
[TAKI] We spend most of our time
chillin' at the arcade.
Swing by whenever
you're in the mood.
After all, just 'cause
you didn't join us,
doesn't mean
we can't be friends!
[THUG 19A]
That friggin' hurt, girly.
You're gonna pay for that!
What? Mm!
[TAKEDA grunts, groans]
[DELINQUENT 19B] I'll teach you
to sucker punch the boss!
[THUG 19A groans]
[MINAKO] Jeez, Taki,
didn't I teach you
to never turn your back
on an enemy?
[JUNICHIRO]
That you, Face Punch?
Man, long time no see!
Whoa, Mr. Kagami?
Wait. How is it
you two know each other?
That's a long story,
but the cliffsnotes version is
he taught at
my school for a bit.
He's actually the one
who straightened me out
and set me
on the path I'm on now.
[gasps]
Oh, I see. Well, we gotta go.
Hold on a sec,
I need to talk to you.
I don't know why
you re-formed the group,
but I think
you should reconsider.
I kinda hate to
tell you this, Minako.
But, I only have time
for current team members,
not some washed up
leader who ditched us.
Excuse us.
[DELINQUENT 19A, 19B, 19C]
Peace out. See ya.
Taki. You've probably
figured this out,
but Taki was
part of the gang I lead.
That was the original
Black Oracle.
She worried more than anyone
else about her friends,
and was the most upset
when I disbanded the group.
She's recreated
what I took from her
by finding kids who have
nowhere else to go.
I get why she's doing it.
But that life's
way too dangerous.
Her sister's a former member,
too, and she asked me
to help get Taki
off the streets.
But like you saw,
she doesn't listen to anyone.
Least of all, me.
[JUNICHIRO]
Hmm.
[doorbell rings]
[MAIL MAN 19A]
Delivery!
[JUNICHIRO]
What is this?
That's a special invitation
to the 5th Queens mini-concert!
Tickets to these things
sell out stupid-fast!
How did you get this?
By taking it out of
the mail man's hand?
And it says "plus one"!
I can't believe
you did this for me!
You're getting
ahead of yourself.
I never said you were going,
or even that I was going.
Oh. I think we both know
deep down that we're going.
Uh! Sounds like a good time!
[JUNICHIRO]
Wow! The hype is real!
[SUZUNE]
Yeah, I told you!
Nothing is more popular than
the 5th Queens right now!
Which is kinda hard
to believe seeing as
they're just
five middle school girls,
but they sure know
how to put on a show!
Look at this crowd!
[JUNICHIRO]
What's she doing here?
Hey! Let's go find
a better spot to watch!
--Come on!
--Yeah.
[CROWD cheers]
[music plays]
Ready? Okay, it's time
to start the show!
[CROWD cheers]
[5TH QUEENS singing]
[cheers]
Oh yeah!
[singing continues]
[JUNICHIRO]
Well, I think it's official.
I'm a 5th Queens fanboy now!
Thank you so much
for coming to see us!
[CROWD cheers]
That was so much better
than watching on TV!
And they're
way too cute in person!
[cell phone rings]
Unknown caller?
Must be a wrong number.
Uh, hello?
[NAGARE ON PHONE]
Hi, Mr. Kagami?
This is Nagare Komiya. You met
my sister Taki the other day?
Yeah, I did.
How did you end up
with my number, though?
[NAGARE] Oh, well, Minako
put me in contact with you.
I was hoping we could
talk about my sister.
That's why I sent you
the invite to the concert.
Did you happen to make it?
[JUNICHIRO]
Huh?
[NAGARE] Excuse me!
Are you Mr. Kagami?
That is what they tell me.
[gasps]
I'm sorry I called you
out of the blue.
But you're the only one
who can help me.
Whoa. Hold on a second.
You're her sister?
Please excuse the outfit,
I didn't have time to change.
Oh, don't worry about it.
I totally get that.
[JUNICHIRO] It's the being-
related-to-a-gang-leader
I don't understand.
Then I'll get
right to the point.
I have to ask you for a favor.
What kind of favor?
Please convince Taki
to leave the gang!
It's awful. She just--
She refuses to listen to me
no matter what I say.
I know what Minako was like
back in the old days,
but you managed
to get through to her.
That's why if anyone stands a
chance at saving Taki, it's you!
Yeah, but the circumstances
are pretty different.
And she does have the right
to do what she wants.
I understand that
I'm asking a lot of you.
And I don't expect you
to do this for free.
Please! I'll give you
anything you want
if you do this for me! Anything!
But why does it matter
to you when you know
it means so much to her?
Come on, you used to be
a part of a gang, too, right?
Well yeah, but it's dangerous
and I just get worried.
[TAKI]
It's "dangerous"?
[gasps]
Taki.
If I told you show business
was dangerous,
would that be enough
to make you quit?
'Cause I'm thinkin'
that's not the case.
But then, I would never
say something like that,
because I know everyone
belongs somewhere.
And once someone
has found that place,
they'll never be able
to live without it,
and no one has the right
to take it away!
[JUNICHIRO]
Hmm.
I've supported you because
I truly believe your place
has always been
in front of an audience.
So tell me.
Why are you trying to
take the place where
I belong away from me?
You've got it wrong.
I'm not trying
to hurt you at all.
No matter what the situation,
I'd never do that.
[JUNICHIRO] You know, now is
the perfect time to quit.
The Black Oracle gang you knew
doesn't exist anymore.
Maybe it's time
you let go of its memory.
[gasps]
[TAKI]
I'll never do that.
[JUNICHIRO]
Hmm.
[TAKI]
I know what I had is gone.
But as long as I'm around,
what it meant to me
will continue to live on.
That's what I stand for
as the only remaining
Black Oracle member.
No one takes that from me!
[JUNICHIRO]
That's the spirit!
[BOTH]
Huh?
There's nothing
I like more than hearing
a strong character
give a good monologue.
Otaku honor decrees I have
to side with you, so yeah!
After hearing your speech,
I'm afraid I have no choice
but to join Black Oracle Neo.
You can't be serious!
And now that I'm a member,
it's my duty to help you
create the best place to be.
As a teacher, you're supposed
to set a good example.
You can't join a street gang!
Well, I believe if someone
wants to do something,
they should do it. That's my
style "as a teacher."
Here's your last chance.
Why are you so opposed,
"Idol Sister"?
Mmm.
If you're not going to tell us,
then there's
nothing left to discuss
and I'm taking
your sister's side.
You're on your own
in this endeavor.
Fine, but I'm not giving up.
[JUNICHIRO]
Hrm.
[TAKI]
They closed down?
[DELINQUENT 19C]
I was worried about this.
I think after we started
hanging out here,
fewer people were coming by.
No. This is supposed
to be our spot!
Well there's no point in us
standing here anymore.
[ALL]
Huh?
[JUNICHIRO]
Let's roll out!
But where are we going?
I know of an arcade
that's open twenty-four-seven.
Sound good?
[DELINQUENT 19C]
I hate to tell you,
but this is just
an abandoned building.
[JUNICHIRO] I thought something
like this might happen.
So, we've got a lot
of work ahead of us.
You ready?
Ready to do what?
You're not making sense.
[JUNICHIRO] We'll build
our own arcade right here.
[ALL]
You're kidding!
Finding a hangout
is whatever.
But creating your
own place is way past cool!
[TAKI] Y'know, this team has
been together for a while now,
but we've never done anything
like an actual group before.
It's kinda fun!
[JUNICHIRO]
I'm glad to hear it.
Hey, I was wondering.
You don't hate your sister
or anything, right?
No, of course not.
Actually, we used to hang out
together all the time.
Ever since we were kids,
she wanted to be a singer,
and I'm really happy
she was able to do it,
even though she moved away.
With all the fame and fans,
you never thought of
becoming an idol yourself?
Not at all. I'd sing
and dance with her
when she wanted
to play pretend, sure.
That's what sisters do.
But it never really caught
my interest outside of that.
I've always been happier
spending time with my friends,
or just walking around town.
Stuff like that.
[JUNICHIRO]
Hmm.
This means a lot.
[JUNICHIRO]
Hm?
You're fun, that's all.
Thanks for joining.
I'm just doing my part,
but, you're welcome.
[phone ringing]
[CEO]
Komi-Ryu, baby! Guess what?
I booked you the gig!
[NAGARE gasps]
Get ready for prime-time
because you're playing the lead!
Wait. I really got the part?
[CEO] You sure did!
Of course, it helped
that you grew up
with a twin sister.
It's what Twin Moon
Princesses is all about!
Better get ready!
You're going to be the face
of all our
advertisements coming up!
You should be excited.
What's the matter?
Oh, nothing.
This is a dream come true!
[birds chirping]
[SUZUNE] Bro, there's an
emergency, come quick!
I'm here. Do you need
the first aid kit?
It's not me.
Komi-Ryu vanished!
What do you expect
me to do about that?
I expect you
to be sensitive.
She's missing the interview
I want to watch!
Komi-Ryu will
be with us shortly,
and we apologize for
the unforeseen delay.
I can't believe
she would do this to me.
[door bell rings]
Bro, will you answer that?
I can't leave
when Komi-Ryu needs me.
Okay!
[JUNICHIRO]
Yeah? Can I help you?
You said we should
do what we want.
Isn't that right?
Yeah, sounds like me.
So what brings you
out here? Coulda called.
I'm here because
you have to get Taki
to leave Black Oracle Neo!
Don't you see? You're the
only person she listens to.
So I'm not leaving
until you agree to help me.
Hm. You're persistent,
I'll give you that.
Aren't you supposed to
be somewhere right now?
Skipping an interview
for your sis. I'm shocked.
No, you've got it all wrong!
I'm doing this for myself.
If things stay
the way they are now,
well then, I...
I'll quit! I'll leave my job
as a singer for good!
[JUNICHIRO]
Mmm.
[TAKI] This is Taki Komiya,
the leader of
Black Oracle Neo coming at ya!
I'm really glad
Junichiro changed his mind
about joining us.
But I've got no idea
what my sister's up to.
Next episode, we're gonna
find out how Nagare
managed to land her dream job!
We're also gonna sing
the Family Rangers theme song,
which is a classic!
Period twenty,
"The Twin Idol."
Nagare, just forget about
what happened back then.
I've already found
the place where I belong.