[JUNICHIRO]
I have YD.
You say you've
never heard of it?
What? I like wearing yukata
on dates? Or yummy dinners?
Wrong! It's a
debilitating illness
where you can only do
what you yearn to do.
[ANCIENT DRAGON roars]
Let's go! Ready, Luce?
You bet!
3, 2, and 1. It's the end
of the line, Ancient Dragon!
[ANCIENT DRAGON growls]
I call on the power of the
Sky Spirits and implore thee
to Shield my body and
Strike down my foes!
Skill charging complete.
Spiritual Guard Skill Activated.
My level 4 Spirit Bind
will hold him in place!
[ANCIENT DRAGON roars]
Okay, First! It's your turn!
[JUNICHIRO]
Skill charging complete!
My unblockable Dual Wield
Flurry Skill is activated!
You're going down!
I've got him now, Luce.
Watch this!
[JUNICHIRO yells]
Bullet Sword Infinity!
[ANCIENT DRAGON roars]
[MAN A] You're telling
me they defeated
the Ancient Dragon by
themselves? I don't buy it!
How could two
people beat one of
the most difficult
quests in Uroboros?
[MAN B] I heard they finished
off that freakin' dragon
in world record
time, no less!
Someone told me that they took
out a 20-man raiding party.
I thought the rumor was bull,
but maybe these
two're the real deal.
I wish I could be
as strong as them.
Godspeed Red Knight
the First is my hero.
And Luce the Ironclad
Nun is so graceful!
[JUNICHIRO] I thought the
Ancient Dragon would be harder
to take down, but we
beat it, no sweat.
It appears there's not much left
we can do together in Uroboros.
But look at how much we
did get done this last year.
And none of it would
have been possible
if we weren't
working together.
No one ever noticed me,
let alone offered to help,
until you pledged to
wield your sword beside me.
It took a lot of grinding,
but now you've got
all your skills maxed
and all that awesome gear.
Well, thank you,
'cause there's no way
I could've cleared
that stuff on my own,
let alone finished every single
small party quest in the game.
We still have one last
thing we could do.
It'd be a good challenge.
You're not talking
about tomorrow's
Mega Battle Event, are you?
I think you misread the
email about it, because that's
only for large teams.
We're not eligible to join.
We are extremely proud to
announce the once-in-a-lifetime
"Battle of Uro," a Large
Squad Mega Battle Event
For Quest Teams with
35 Members or More.
Lame! 35? Fine then!
[LUCE]
Uh--?
[JUNICHIRO] Listen, Luce,
there's no way I'm giving up
without finishing
all the quests.
Let's unlock one final trophy.
What do ya say?
Um. Okay. If we can.
Good! All right. Start up
a private training room.
I'll meet you there
in just about 3 hours.
Uh, but First...
Don't worry. I know
where to recruit our squad.
I'm gonna log out now, but I'll
be back before you miss me!
Oh, you have to go?
Yeah?
You haven't been hanging around
too much after quests lately.
Is something going on
outside the game?
Sorry, I have been busy.
No! Don't apologize!
I shouldn't have asked
about your I.R.L. stuff. It's
totally rude. I'm so mortified.
Hey, don't worry about it! We've
got bigger fish to fry anyway,
so I'll see you in a few hours
to train for tomorrow's event!
Later!
[LUCE groans]
[JUNICHIRO yawns]
Okay. I guess I
should go to work.
[JUNICHIRO sighs]
[MAKINA]
Hey, Mr. Kagami!
Eh? 'Sup, Twin-Tails?
Am I too late for class
again or something?
Y'know, you probably
shouldn't shout at a teacher.
Rude. But whatever,
I just wanted to let you know
Sachiko is officially
back at school now.
Great. Are you gonna pitch me
a plot for this week's ep?
Even though you yourself
are a complete delinquent,
you've made some impressive
achievements as a mentor.
For example, you've
helped Miss Chinami
improve her grades tremendously.
And you've convinced her
to speak in public for the
first time since grade school!
An amazing feat!
You've also somehow
managed to get Icho Academy's
most notorious truant and
malcontent to come to classes.
You've earned formal praise
from Madam Chairperson
as well as myself.
You hit your head?
[MAKINA] I'm giving you
a compliment, weirdo!
Why do you have to make
everything difficult?
Thanks, I guess.
Can I go?
I'm not finished.
Sachiko wasn't the only
truant you needed
to bring back.
You shouldn't just
rest on your laurels.
You have a responsibility
to class 2-3,
and the administration
expects your support,
Mister Kagami.
Hm. Now I wonder. Was there
a point to all of that noise?
[SEIJURO grunts]
[KISAKI] Hold that pose...
The details of your muscles
are going to make my next manga
look absolutely wonderful!
Can you please hurry it up?
My arms are getting worn out.
That pose too tough for you,
big man? Oh, well. That's fine.
Hm. On to the next one!
The next?
Now, maid, come join muscles!
Okay!
[SEIJURO groans]
Stop whining!
You make it sound awful.
Like I'm some kind
of heavy old maid!
[SEIJURO] Mm... What did
I get myself into?
Tell me there's some sort of
logical explanation for this.
Kisaki only agreed to
come back to class
if she's allowed to
work on her manga,
so Mister Kagami said
we should just go along
with whatever she wants us
to do, no questions asked.
So he's bribing her
to come to school
and turned our classroom
into this circus?
Don't think of it
as a bribe.
It's more like, manga is
what she yearns to do,
so he wants to encourage her
and get her to come to school.
Well, when you
put it like that...
"Classroom of the Terminus"
is my favorite book right now,
so I'm psyched to see her work!
[SUZUNE and KANAN]
Hm?
Eyes up here.
We're gonna do work today.
[students groan]
Today's lesson is different!
I woke up with a revelation.
You need The History of Warfare!
[students gasp]
[SUZUNE] War history?
What's he talking about?
Man, I think he is definitely
getting us into something weird.
Mr. Kagami's a genius,
so I know he's got
a good reason for
lecturing us on this!
Yeah! I'm sure he's
got a good plan!
[KISAKI exhales]
Sure.
[SUZUNE] Excuse me, brother,
but don't you teach physics?
Pop quiz, hot shot:
How would you explain
the definition of life?
[SUZUNE]
Uh... Huh?
I want the answer
for "what is life?"
[SUZUNE] What does that
have to do with anything?
So, you don't know, huh?
Well then, let me
explain it to you.
Life by its very
definition is battle!
[SUZUNE]
Uh...
As you all move forward
and graduate, you will
undoubtedly encounter devious
foes and colleagues alike!
If you expect to defeat
the nefarious people
in your life, you'll need
an understanding
of warfare, passed down
to us by our ancestors!
[students gasp]
Okay. That doesn't
sound completely insane,
but I bet you've got some
kind of ulterior motive.
You're welcome to formally
register your complaints
with me after class. In the
meantime, if you would all
please open up your laptops
so the lesson can begin.
Wait, so what in the heck
is a You-rob-urr-oz?
This is Uroboros.
Isn't this, like, some kind
of online game for nerds?
You've already been registered,
your characters have
been customized,
and I went ahead and
picked out your roles!
So go ahead and input the
provided user name and password.
Alright! The cyberspace
battlefield awaits you!
[SUZUNE shudders]
[KANAN gasps]
[KIRIKO moans]
[SEIJURO groans]
[KISAKI]
Ah.
[STUDENTS]
What the heck is going on?
[JUNICHIRO]
Welcome one and all!
You are now part of Japan's
most popular MMORPG, Uroboros.
How are you going
to teach us history
when we're playing
a fantasy game?
This is kind of
creeping me out.
I mean, these characters you've
created look exactly like us.
There's no way my mom
would ever let me play
an online game at home.
This is gonna be awesome!
That skull makes you
look really cool, Seijuro.
Uh... Yeah?
OK, class.
I need you to listen up.
I brought you together
here for a single purpose.
Tomorrow, they're holding a Mega
Event called "Battle of Uro."
I'll be the General,
you'll be my army,
and everything that stands
in our way will be dead!
Gross. How are you going to
pretend that's school work? Ah?!
You can't understand
the history of warfare
if you don't get your
hands a little dirty.
You have to learn how
to fight for yourself!
Say what?
[JUNICHIRO]
I'm allowing you to simulate
actual battle theory
in a safe environment!
To learn real-world
lessons without injury!
Tomorrow's battle is more than
some video game trophy grab.
The point is,
if you can win here,
then you can
win everywhere!
For your future!
Fight and win!
[JUNICHIRO] Not to
mention you'll be helping
me and Luce complete
our quest list!
Man, teach, you make it
sound really exciting.
Wow, there's so many.
How did he manage
to round up all these new
teammates for us so quickly?
Whoa, where'd that
pretty girl come from?
She's not in our class.
Hey, there,
glad you're here!
Guys, I'd like to introduce
you all to my partner.
She's seen me through a lot
of my battles in Uroboros
and made this lesson
possible. Meet Luce!
She's fought by my
side this past year.
She's a powerhouse, and she'll
be my Lieutenant tomorrow.
Hi. It's a pleasure, everyone!
[STUDENTS] The pleasure
is all ours, we assure you!
So, uh, what are we supposed
to do now that we're here?
He said we're
going to a battle,
so there will be some
kind of fight, obviously.
Then I don't want
this stupid sword.
My mitts are all
I need, sweetheart.
I really doubt it's gonna
be that kind of fight.
Uh, hey, Kanan?
Isn't there usually a way
to like modify our
outfits in these games?
I think there usually is.
Awesome! Do you wanna go help
me pick out a new costume?
I'm coming with you! I could
kill him for dressing me
in something so trashy!
I'm his sister!
Are you kidding?
That outfit is totally you!
Please don't say that!
[LUCE] Um, First,
they seem more worried
about their outfits
than the game.
Are you sure you can trust
all of these outsiders?
Aren't you concerned
that one might
find out about
your offline life?
Oh, don't worry.
They all already know.
I'm otaku, but I'm also
a high school teacher,
and I recruited these kids
from my class for the event.
There's no reason to worry.
Oh, so you, the great First,
are a teacher in real life.
But that doesn't make your
students trustworthy, does it?
Maybe not. And actually,
a few of them are delinquents.
Regardless, I've decided
to put my faith in them.
[LUCE]
Huh?
By doing so, it allows us to
do more interesting things
than boring textbook lessons.
[LUCE]
Who knew?
That's why he doesn't hang
around as much anymore.
I thought maybe he suspected...
[JUNICHIRO]
Hey, Luce!
Ready to whip these
brats into shape?
Oh! Yeah, alright!
[JUNICHIRO]
So there, class.
Long story short,
in order to make
the fullest sense
of your training,
you'll need to understand
what your role is gonna be,
and how you'll coordinate
with one another in order
to maintain proper positioning
and battle efficiency.
Um, so. Mr. Kagami?
I think you're speaking
a foreign language 'cause
I didn't get any of that.
Yeah, I'm excited to
learn, but I'm afraid
you're not making a
whole lot of sense.
Okay, since it's
apparently too complicated,
a demonstration should help
make things a bit more clear.
[indistinct chatter]
How about this? I want you
to hit me as hard as you can.
If any one of you can inflict
even a single point of damage
to either Luce or myself, then
every last member of the class
will earn a homework exemption
for the rest of the month!
[excited chatter]
One lucky hit and the rest of
the month is smooth sailing!
I am never gonna
do homework again!
Whatever, I'm not scared of
a couple of computer geeks!
I'm ready to take you both on!
[SEIJURO roars]
Best lesson ever!
This is gonna be
the most fun I've had in ages!
[SEIJURO] Here I come,
otaku teacher!
You won't score hits against
an advanced opponent
with just a battle cry
and brute force!
How do you like
this battle cry?
Horizon Sla--!
Your wind-up is way
too big and slow,
so any seasoned combatant is
gonna dodge that in their sleep.
You!
Also, class, you'd do
very well to remember
that after a heavy
missed strike,
your back is left totally
open to an attack.
Skill activate, summon mythical
beast! Mon-mon-momonga!
[STUDENTS]
Ahhh...!
Mon Mon, go!
No! You killed it!
Beast Master-type characters
have multiple summons
with different uses
and abilities.
Finding the right beast
for each situation is key!
My sweet monster...
Let's see if you can handle
this one! Skill activate!
Mysterious... Dance!
Paralyze Arrow!
I can't move!
Hey, Potatoes, you're
not supposed to dance
on the front lines. As a
Dancer, your primary role
is support, so you should
stay near the rear guard!
Yep! I understand now.
Seijuro, I hate to admit it,
but none of us are going
to hit him if we keep
attacking one at a time.
One day I'll be good
enough to be able
to take him down on my own!
Can you go ahead
and put down
that chip on your
shoulder for today?
[SEIJURO grunts]
So, you suggest
teaming up, huh?
Now you're gettin' it.
We move quick, I run point,
you cover my back.
He can't take us both.
I'm down for whatever you
suggest. I just hope we can
wipe that idiotic smirk
off Mister Kagami's face.
Sounds good to me.
Okay then. Ready? Set!
And let's go!
[SUZUNE and SEIJURO yell]
I see they've teamed up
to fight a stronger foe.
Not a bad tactic at all!
[SUZUNE and SEIJURO yell]
But then again...
[SEIJURO and SUZUNE groan]
When you're challenging
an overwhelming force,
even a strong tactic
won't be enough.
[KISAKI]
Hey, teach!
What if the team is not two,
but actually three of us?
[JUNICHIRO gasps]
Black Magic, Deep Blue.
I'm coming for you--
[LUCE]
Spell Break.
[KISAKI groans]
The element of surprise
can be very effective indeed.
But you were too confident
and forgot that the First
has a partner fighting
alongside him as well.
Regrettably.
Man, she took Kisaki down!
Yeah, I'm not even
gonna embarrass myself.
Now don't freak
out on me. Heh.
After all, you still
have to strike
if you want to
land a lucky blow!
If you make the attempt
and it gets you nowhere,
then use your head
and change up the moves
you face your challenge with!
In this game, and in life,
that's the most
effective strategy!
I've had it. Let's take 'im.
But Seijuro...
He's humiliated us. We can't
let him get away with this
without getting
knocked down a peg.
You're not wrong, but rushing
at them headlong with our eyes
down like a herd of bulls
isn't going to work either.
Watch it!
Pairs aren't enough. We
definitely need teams of four.
Oh, I bet my razor
sharp dancing moves
would work as a great decoy!
OK, everybody's
thinking fast now,
but first we've gotta
break those two up.
[indistinct chatter]
[JUNICHIRO and LUCE chuckle]
[chatter continues]
Are you all satisfied
with your plan yet?
Good, then bring it on!
Let's hit 'em
with all we got, guys!
[various yells and cries]
[students groan]
Congrats! You kinda
survived basic training!
Now's where the fun
really begins!
[monsters growl]
[SEIJURO]
What the heck is that?
[KIRIKO] Whatever they
are, they don't look
like they wanna
make friends with us!
[LUCE] The mob you
see approaching you
is controlled by the A.I.
Tomorrow's event is competitive,
but it's PVE, not PVP,
so we'll need to train against
large groups of enemies.
What's important
here is that everybody
gets on the same strategic page.
You need to pay attention to the
direction of the battle and take
special care to heed the advice
that Luce and I offer you.
[LUCE] During a large-scale
raid, communication is key.
You have to make sure to execute
your attacks at the right time
and in response to
both enemies and allies.
Follow our orders
and we'll all experience
the spoils of victory together!
Now's your chance.
You can take out
some of your aggression
on these ugly suckers!
Don't be afraid to
go all out on 'em!
Ready, team?
[STUDENTS]
Yeah!
Now, soldiers! Attack!
[STUDENTS yell]
[roars and yells]
[SUZUNE yells]
[SEIJURO yells]
[monster roars]
Whoa! I got him!
We couldn't even
scratch my brother,
but we're doing fine now.
We're totally gonna mop
the floor with these clowns!
Ready?
[STUDENTS]
Oh, yeah!
[distant yelling
and grunting]
[JUNICHIRO and LUCE chuckle]
[distant yelling
and grunting]
[JUNICHIRO]
Front line, formation 2!
Back line, assault 3!
Mythical Beast!
[monsters roar]
Hold on.
That's kinda odd.
Is something wrong?
I seem to be
missing a student.
Huh?
I'm not sure. There's 33
students in my class,
but only 32 on the
battlefield right now.
I don't understand how I
could have missed someone.
[KISAKI] Are you actually
that dense, Junichiro?
There is still another truant.
Remember? I wasn't the only
student in your class that
had an attendance problem.
[JUNICHIRO]
Mm.
[KISAKI] I'm sure you've
never properly taken roll
since you started
at Icho Academy.
It's not a surprise
you didn't notice.
Well. With me and Luce,
that's 34 of us, but we're still
one short of the requirement
for tomorrow's event.
I know what I need to do! I'm
gonna go to that kid's house
and drag 'em to school
with my bare hands!
What? The battle's tomorrow!
You'll never get them
here in time to train!
[JUNICHIRO]
Logging out!
He can be a grade-A
jumbo fool, huh?
But I guess you probably
knew that already.
[LUCE]
Mm...
[JUNICHIRO] Twin-Tailed Weirdo
emailed me that roll sheet
the other day. I should be
able to use that to figure out
which kid is missing
and their address.
Koutaro Araki.
Must be this dude.
[ARAKI'S MOTHER] Thank you.
It's so thoughtful of you
to come all this way
to check on my child.
[JUNICHIRO]
No problem, Ma'am.
[ARAKI'S MOTHER]
Uh, would you like some tea?
No, that's alright.
Thank you, though.
I'd appreciate it if you'd
direct me to your son's room.
[ARAKI'S MOTHER]
Upstairs to the right, but...
[JUNICHIRO] Thank you
very much for your help.
So, is there anything
wrong with him?
[ARAKI'S MOTHER] Well, he's
been locked up in his room
for the past year.
He hardly even speaks to me,
let alone anyone else.
It's terrible.
Don't you worry! I'll have
him attending school again
whether he likes it or not!
[JUNICHIRO] Otherwise I can kiss
tomorrow's Mega Battle goodbye!
[ARAKI'S MOTHER] Wow,
you are such a passionate
and young teacher!
So, this is
your son's room?
Electronic security?
Jeez, you weren't exaggerating.
He really is locked in there!
Yes, and I'm afraid
the circumstances
are a little complicated.
[JUNICHIRO]
Uh--?
I don't know if it would
really be of any assistance,
but I could call out
Koutaro's name for you.
Thanks for offering,
but that's really okay.
There's no time to
worry about formalities--
I'm just gonna hack this keycode
panel and get that door open.
[beeping]
[click]
[JUNICHIRO]
Heh!
Koutaro! My name is
Mr. Junichiro Kagami,
and you're a truant--
[JUNICHIRO gasps]
[LUCE gasps]
Luce? What?
The First?
What are you doing here?
[LUCE yelps]
[JUNICHIRO]
Wait, Luce is really...?
No, never mind that.
I thought this was...
Um, Mr. Kagami, please meet...
...my beautiful son, Koutaro.
[JUNICHIRO stammers]
[JUNICHIRO] Godspeed Red Knight
the First, here! What's up?
What a shocker for
me to discover firsthand
that Luce is really the
truant Koutaro Araki!
Next episode, I got the missing
spot on our battle team
filled by you-know-who
with a little trickery.
But just when I thought we
were good to go, Luce runs off!
Period 10,
"The Melancholy of Koutaro."
Luce, no matter where you run,
I'll be here for you.
You are my awesome
questing partner, after all!