[JUNICHIRO]
I have YD.
You say you've
never heard of it?
What? I like wearing yukata
on dates? Or yummy dinners?
Wrong! It's a
debilitating illness
where you can only do
what you yearn to do.
[laughter and jeering]
[YOU RED POND]
♪ Amazing grace ♪
♪ How sweet the sound
that saved a wretch... ♪
[JUNICHIRO grunts]
Man. I am so glad that's over.
[SUZUNE]
Hey, bro.
Huh? Hey there,
sis. What's up?
[JUNICHIRO]
Uh...
Actually, I was
looking for you.
I've got someone here
I want you to meet.
Oh, yeah, this girl has me
for physics, doesn't she?
Yep. Allow me to introduce
my friend Kanan Chinami.
She's got some physics
questions, and since I said
you were my brother, she was
hoping you could help her.
Are you kidding?
I already finished teaching
my classes for the day.
[SUZUNE]
Hnn--hyah!
Are we about to have a problem?
Oh no, everything's
just dandy, thank you.
That's right. Do you always
have to go out of your way
to make my life so difficult?
Do you always have
to wave a bat at me
just because I'm being myself?
[SUZUNE] Whatever. Kanan
needs to make a great score
on her next physics exam,
and you're her best shot
at achieving that.
So you are going to help her.
Why do I have to help her?
I just wanna go home
and work on my blog. I'm losing
followers left and right.
[SUZUNE] It's your
job to help her.
Her grade's gotta be in
the top 10 in her class.
If it's not, she has to
miss You Red Pond's concert.
[JUNICHIRO]
You who what?
[SUZUNE] You Red Pond
is the name
of Kanan's favorite
American singer.
She's desperate to
go to the concert.
So you're gonna have
to forget about your blog
and help her
get her grade up.
I'm not getting what
her grades have to do
with her going to a concert.
Kanan's parents are super
strict about school,
so she really needs to
wow them with her grades
to be able to go. So?
Hm. Fine.
I guess since I'm supposed to
be a teacher and everything.
Eh... Can you tell me
what you need help with?
[JUNICHIRO gasps]
Great Scott!
She just texted me.
"I don't understand the part
about how physics works
or why and stuff."
[JUNICHIRO stammers]
[JUNICHIRO] Am I the only one
who saw how weird that was?
So, uh, yeah, what's the deal
with that whole exchange?
[SUZUNE] Do not make me hit you
for asking a stupid question.
[JUNICHIRO] She never speaks?
[SUZUNE] Nope. Back in
middle school, Kanan and I
were classmates and good
friends, but she's never
uttered a word to me
or anyone since then.
[JUNICHIRO]
Hm.
Kids can be cruel.
They would make fun of
her a lot for her voice.
So she stopped talking and only
communicates through texts now.
[JUNICHIRO]
Hmm...
Also, it doesn't help
that she's really pretty.
Along with the "no talking"
thing, she's kinda famous.
[SUZUNE blows]
Mm... Now people treat
her like a challenge.
Loads of guys have tried dumb
stuff to get her to talk.
They've brought her flowers,
taken her on dates.
They're so cocky,
but no one's convinced her
they deserve to hear
the sound of her voice yet.
Nobody can get
her to talk, huh?
It seems like a lot of
hassle that could easily
be taken care of if she
would just talk. Y'know?
Oh, please don't be
that way, Junichiro.
It's supposed to be
a big secret, but...
Her voice actually
sounds like...
[JUNICHIRO]
Whaaaaat?
Why didn't you mention the
most important fact until now?!
Kanan has absolutely no choice
in the matter! She must speak!
Hmph!
[SUZUNE groans]
[indistinct chatter]
[JUNICHIRO] Miss Kanan Chinami.
Miss Kanan Chinami.
Please report to the
science storage room.
I repeat, Class 2-3...
All right, Kanan.
Let's conduct an experiment.
My sister finally
told me your secret.
And that look confirms it.
So I've set up
a first-rate dialogue
recording session for you.
Oh, the microphone?
It's vitally important
that I hear your anime voice.
I've taken the storage room and
made it into a recording studio.
I hope you realize I've
gone to a lot of effort.
The acoustics
are perfection. Hm?
Huh? You wonder why I
would go to such lengths?
Because it is
absolutely imperative
that I hear your voice!
There are over 2,000 voice
actors working in the field.
But amongst those,
probably fewer than 10
are actually the "chosen ones."
A natural anime voice
is so rare even otaku
like me seldom hear one.
If only you would whisper
something in my ear!
I would give my life to
hear such a pure sound!
But then which line
would I like to hear?
How would I ever
be able to choose?
How can a father
pick a favorite child?
Maybe Sergeant Saunders'
signature line, "Bakyuun"?
And maybe after that... Huh?
[JUNICHIRO]
Hm?
[JUNICHIRO] That is correct.
None at all. Worry-free.
You're beginning to
understand how important
your voice is to a
true otaku like me.
Behold! The super
priceless recording script
for episode one of "Magical
Cannon Girl Bura-Kura"!
So are you ready to begin?
[JUNICHIRO groans]
[JUNICHIRO grunts]
All right, Kanan Chinami.
Your voice is the prize,
and I'm playing to win.
Yes! Everything is going
exactly as I'd planned.
It's time to start the lesson!
Mornin', jerk. So what did
you say to Kanan yesterday?
A bunch of stuff. Did she
tell you something was wrong?
I've been texting her all day
and she's only replied
with silence. Total silence.
"Silence"?
That is an unexpected
complication.
You already knew that she was
super sensitive about her voice.
You should be teaching her
and not harassing her about it!
[JUNICHIRO] That can't be
what you really think, is it?
[SUZUNE]
Uhh...
[JUNICHIRO] Are you sure it's
best to let her go on like this?
Well, maybe not, But how could
we convince her otherwise?
Okay, that settles it. You get
to help me teach this lesson.
[SUZUNE]
Hm?
[JUNICHIRO] We are talking about
a priceless anime voice here.
As if I'm going to let a
miracle like that pass me by!
Why do I feel like
you're roping me
into a scheme I'll
regret in the end?
[TV REPORTER]
Next up in the news hour...
You Red Pond, the world famous
singer, has begun her world tour
tonight in Miami, Florida, USA,
and venues are selling out.
She will be
visiting 130 countries
with her amazing voice. Rum--
[JUNICHIRO] So the physics
struggle is real, huh?
There's only one week
left before the test.
How much do you think you
can learn all on your own?
And I hate to be a
downer, but it looks
like you're not
making much progress.
[JUNICHIRO] No response at all?
Awfully cold of you.
[DOOR VOICE] You must say
the password, gero gero.
Oh, looks like I forgot
to mention something.
The doors in the library
have been modified by me.
The locks are voice-activated,
but don't worry.
All you have to do is say
Sergeant Saunders' famous
catchphrase and they'll ope--
Hm. So there's still some
work to do on this project.
Oh, Mrs. Chinami, you don't seem
old enough to have a teenager!
That's kind of
you to say, sir!
It's easy when it's the truth!
Be careful not to
flatter me too much!
I didn't think Kanan would
have such a great mom!
Hey, girl! Are you
surprised to see us?
We were all waiting for you!
[KANAN'S MOTHER] Kanan,
come sit with your teacher!
If I'd been expecting Kanan's
teacher this afternoon,
I would've prepared a
special dinner for all of you!
Please, it's my fault,
I assure you.
There's no reason
to scold Miss Kanan.
I found myself suddenly
overcome with the need
to help this eager student, and
the whole plan was last minute,
so I didn't give her a
chance to prepare you!
Kanan's struggled with
physics for so long.
She's lucky to have
such a dedicated teacher.
With your assistance,
I know she'll rise
to the top of her class!
Don't worry--
you can count on me!
I am, after all, the number
one physics teacher.
[KANAN'S MOTHER] How perfectly
charming and dramatic!
[SUZUNE and KANAN'S
MOTHER laugh]
We're not gonna abandon you.
I anticipated a reaction
like this from you.
Suzune, you're on.
[SUZUNE]
Hm!
Since she's used to speaking
with you, Suzune will translate
so you can let us know
how you really feel.
Now, please, go ahead
and let it all out.
"Can you please leave
and get out of my life?
In case you hadn't noticed,
I actually have to study.
I don't want anything to do
with you or your schemes."
[JUNICHIRO] Are you sure
that's what you want?
[SUZUNE hums]
"Neither my fingers nor your
sister's voice stuttered.
Besides, why did the two of you
come all the way out here?"
Obviously, as a concerned
teacher, it's my duty
to do everything in my power
to improve your test scores.
"Say what?"
What we have here is
a cool anime premise.
I'm the hero and your
voice is a McGuffin
and just like Sergeant Saunders,
I'll fight through
every last challenge.
And just before the
closing credit song begins,
you'll speak to me!
"I would never
make that deal!
It doesn't matter
how special you think
my voice might sound because
I will never speak again!"
[JUNICHIRO]
Like I said...
Are you sure that's really how
you want this all to play out?
You're the one who
said you "have to" go
to You Red Pond's
concert, right?
And correct me if I'm wrong,
but didn't you say
you need to get your grades
up in order to do that?
And we all know you can't
possibly accomplish that
without my generous assistance.
All I'm asking for is
that you kindly allow me
to hear your precious
voice. No biggie.
So, let's make a deal!
"You talk a pretty big game.
I don't see how it's possible
to make the top ten so fast."
[JUNICHIRO] Trust me, my YD
is an asset. It means that
when I actually yearn to do
something, I totally deliver.
How about this? If I can't
tutor you into the top ten,
I will make a solemn
vow to quit. Sound fair?
[SUZUNE gasps]
That's not necessary!
So, whaddaya say?
Heh... Huzzah!
Then we have a deal!
I took the liberty of
analyzing all of your grades
for every subject
since seventh grade.
It seems that where
your previous teachers
failed you is in
your understanding
of quadratic functions
and multipliers.
Naturally, weakness in
those areas would put you
at a disadvantage when studying
wave equations and dynamics,
which ultimately is why your
grades have been going nowhere.
So I built this
especially for you
to work with your shortcomings.
[SUZUNE]
Huh?
[JUNICHIRO] Kanan Quest,
the ultra-personalized
educational video game
built for your success!
This program calculates
your weaknesses
and creates problems instantly!
As your understanding deepens,
the questions intensify.
If you can get past
level 8 in this game,
you should be able to at
least get an 80 on your test.
[JUNICHIRO]
You're stressing too much.
Just like any RPG, if you keep
grinding, you'll get stronger.
Those monsters you're facing now
will be trash mobs in no time.
It'll be easy! Huh?
She says it's not easy
for her, but... hmm.
Hm?
Okay. Think I got it.
[knock at the door]
[JUNICHIRO]
I'm coming in.
Here, since you said it was
too hard, I put together
a brand new custom
system overnight.
[JUNICHIRO] Check out that FMV!
You'd think Square-Enix made it!
Anyway, I call it
Kanan Fantasy 2!
I added a debug function
to help the game
further develop your skills.
It analyzes your
weaknesses in order
to help you overcome them
with clearer questions.
There's no way your
grades won't improve now!
Also, can you believe
those graphics?
Your game is now in high-def 3D,
which adds a level of realism,
depth, and complexity to the
physics problems you encounter.
All of which should
encourage thinking--
[JUNICHIRO grunts]
[JUNICHIRO groans softly]
Did I fall asleep or something?
Sorry, I guess I must've been
pretty exhausted after
the last few nights.
Why are you sorry? In the end,
it's my fault that I haven't
been able to teach you
physics effectively enough--
[JUNICHIRO gasps]
[JUNICHIRO] You have to
get into the top ten...
Otherwise, it wouldn't
be right to accept that.
As an otaku, I take
pride in making
large payments for
things of true value.
I appreciate the
gesture, though.
[JUNICHIRO] You know,
I only got 5 out of 100
on my first physics test.
I thought the whole subject was
boring and irrelevant at first,
but I had this cool idea
to build an "Anywhere Door."
People told me I could never
make something like that
without physics,
so I studied physics
because it was
something I had to do.
I always do what
I "yearn to do,"
but that's not necessarily
what I'm naturally good at,
or even what I can
already accomplish.
In order to realize
a bigger goal,
sometimes I have to do
something I'm bad at.
So in a way,
we're the same.
[BOY A] Whoa, that's
a total anime voice!
[BOY B] Is that
really her real voice?
Are you sure it's not edited?
[BOY C] This is
godlike! Sort of!
[BOY A] Her voice is
in the 2.5th dimension!
[GIRL A] Wow, Kanan,
you're like super popular!
Look at all the comments!
[GIRL B] I always thought
your voice was funny,
but I didn't know what to
call it! "Anime voice," huh?
[GIRLS laugh]
[GIRL B] Huh? The comments
just stopped. What happened?
[GIRL A] They were
coming into the video
like a total flood
until a second ago.
[GIRL C]
Hey, look!
[OTHER GIRLS]
Huh?
[YOU RED POND]
♪ Amazing grace... ♪
[GIRL C] It's You Red Pond's
concert, streaming live!
I guess everyone went
to watch that instead.
[GIRLS ooh and ahh]
[YOU RED POND]
♪ ...that saved a wre-- ♪
[SUZUNE] So. Kanan's
big exam is happening today.
Do you think she'll
do good enough
to be able to go to the concert?
[JUNICHIRO laughs]
You're looking smug!
Hail to the King!
Ah, let me see...
She got up to... Level 10?!
Wow, that's really fantastic!
Yeah, all she had to do was get
past level 8, but she rocked it!
Awesome! So she's actually
prepared to do well on the test?
Why, yes, indeed, she is!
[phone chimes]
Is that my phone?
A little early for a text.
I guess I better get
a move on, and quick!
[JUNICHIRO] Good morning.
Is everything okay?
[phone chimes]
[JUNICHIRO]
Uh, let me just read.
"Mr. Kagami, I hate my voice
more than I can tell you."
Kanan, that's the only thing
I'm sure about with you.
That's why you have such a
fascination with You Red Pond,
isn't it? And why you're
set on going to her concert?
"She saved me.
So ever since that day,
anytime I have the
opportunity to hear her sing,
I'm able to instantly
forget all my problems."
That's fine and dandy,
I suppose,
but that's not really the
issue we're tackling here.
[phone chimes]
"Her voice is so heavenly,
clear, and beautiful,
it's just like the total and
complete opposite of mine."
Well, if you want my opinion,
heavenly, beautiful voices
are totally overrated.
Heh!
♪ Amazing grace,
how sweet the sound ♪
♪ that saved a
wretch like me! ♪
Yeah.
Ya see? I'm glad my voice is
nothing like You Red Pond's.
So you still don't get it.
[ASSORTMENT OF VOICES, ONE AFTER
ANOTHER] And you know what?
[JUNICHIRO] Would you be happy
with any of these voices?
I have a famously bad voice,
but you know what I love?
Karaoke. I go with friends,
and they still have fun
despite the fact that I suck.
You get it now? People like
and enjoy different things.
And that's totally okay.
Miyazaki thinks otaku are
the worst. That doesn't mean
his films are bad or that
something's wrong with me.
All that logical stuff aside,
my point is simple.
We had an agreement.
Will you honor it?
I want to hear your voice,
no matter how it sounds.
[KANAN whimpers]
That's it for today's lesson.
I have really high hopes
for you. I think you're
definitely going to get
that high score you need--
Bakyuun!
[JUNICHIRO gasps]
Good god!
She utterly stunned me!
Now go get 'em,
Anime Girl!
[KANAN giggles]
Uh? What the hell have I done?!
I forgot to record her voice!
[KANAN giggles]
[KANAN] Bakyuun!
This is Kanan Chinami!
I'm talking again,
thanks to Mr. Kagami!
This anime voice is part
of who I am, after all!
In the next episode,
Mr. Kagami meets
a gothic-lolita girl in Akiba.
She is Sachiko Tanaka,
a twisted truant in our class.
Period 8, "The Truant
is a Grand Master."
Her alternate
identity is revealed,
along with her rivalry
with Makina Momozono!
Mr. Kagami's got his
hands full with this one!