This will be the final lesson!
But don't be sad, 'cause I'll
make it a good one!
A tale to echo through the ages!
You'll laugh, you'll cry,
you'll catch YD!
All teachers are looking for
diamonds in the rough,
and I, Junichiro Kagami,
the Ultimate Otaku Teacher,
always find them first!
No way!
Mr. Kagami disappeared
and he still hasn't called you?
That doesn't sound good.
And wait, you can't think of
any place he might run off to?
There's gotta be some clue!
[KOYOMI] There's no
need for you to worry.
Your brother is just fine.
I'm going to take this
to the chairperson.
[ALL]
Huh?
I've had enough! Ugh.
A teacher can't simply
disappear without any notice!
There's no discussion.
This is grounds for dismissal.
Listen, you've
got to fire him!
You don't need to worry
about that. I already have.
Oh, well, good job.
Uh. What?
[knock, knock]
Yes? Come in.
[SUZUNE]
Sorry to interrupt.
Well, hey, Suzune.
[SUZUNE]
We need to talk.
Why, whatever could be
troubling you, Ms. Kagami?
I need more than reassurance.
If you know where
my brother is, tell me!
Okay, can someone
explain the scenario here?
[KOYOMI]
Since my word isn't enough,
I will take care of
this myself. Now, good day.
[GIRLS talking over eachother]
[KOUTARO, KANAN]
Hey, Suzune!
[KIRIKO] Look! She's already
taking off in her car!
We gotta hurry!
She's going to see
my brother, I know it!
That cheater!
Run faster!
[SEIJURO]
You gonna make it?
[KOUTARO]
Uh-huh!
[ALL panting]
You sure
you're gonna make it?
We gotta call a cab!
On it! Well,
that was convenient!
[SUZUNE]
Nice!
Follow the black car
that just took off, okay?
[KIRIKO]
Sorry, gotta prioritize.
Koutaro, get in!
[KOUTARO]
Uh-okay.
[KIRIKO] Seijuro,
do you have your wallet?
Uh yeah, but why?
[KIRIKO]
Yoink!
This is weird.
Where is she going?
Isn't this fun?
[KANAN, KOUTARO]
Mmm.
Uh, sorry.
Can we afford this taxi?
Yeah, I'm a little
low on funds, myself.
Pow! Seijuro's wallet
to the rescue!
[KANAN, KOUTARO]
Huh?
[KIRIKO]
Oh my.
[ALL giggle]
[KOYOMI chuckles]
--[SUZUNE] Wait a sec.
--[KIRIKO] Huh?
[KANAN]
She straight-up disappeared!
[KOUTARO] Well, what are
we supposed to do now?
[JUNICHIRO] For those
of you just tuning in,
you're a little late
to the show,
but I recently met a girl
named Reiko Mukyo.
She's an intern at KEC labs
with the ability
to learn anything after
only watching it once.
Anyway, she was locked up in
some weird institution for ages,
so she needs me to
teach her what "fun" is.
If you really want to
have fun, you gotta learn
to always follow your heart,
no matter what!
It wasn't "okay."
It was the most fun ever!
[KOYOMI]
Is something going on?
Do I know you?
I've come to pick up
your intern, Reiko Mukyo.
[YAMATO]
Oh, yes. About that, um...
I don't wanna
go back to school!
I'm not leaving
and you can't make me!
Oh, that looks bad.
Unfortunately.
It started about an hour ago.
Miss Mukyo, we got
a call from your school
and they said they'll be
coming here to pick you up
in about an hour.
What? No!
But I want to stay here!
You can't take me away
from The Master!
You're acting
like a spoiled brat!
[REIKO]
Hmph!
Some "genius"!
Can you give her a break?
She spent most of her life
in an asylum in the mountains.
She's smart enough
for high school,
but her social skills
aren't there yet.
[REIKO huffs]
Okay, not funny.
Where'd that
trouble-maker run off to?
[MALE VOICE 22A]
Emergency level five.
Didn't we just go through this?
Is it another hacker?
It feels like you get these
every ten minutes.
Wait, it said level five?
We need to do some
more programming magic?
It's worse. An accident.
And bad, too!
[MALE VOICE 22A]
Emergency level five.
[FEMALE STAFF 22A]
Thank goodness, you made it!
The power supply system
readouts are abnormal.
Did you check
if it was a false alarm?
Yes, we went to the power room
to see for ourselves.
[beeping]
[MALE STAFF 23B]
Damn it. Why?
That's not good.
So what will happen if we can't
shut down the power supply?
In just a few minutes,
this entire structure
will likely explode.
[BOTH gasp]
And here we go.
Did Reiko not make it?
I get the feeling
she's in control of all this.
[YAMATO]
Huh?
Oh no.
This whole entire
structure now belongs to me!
No one is allowed to come inside
until I am officially
granted researcher status!
Little brat.
[JUNICHIRO] Hmm.
Well, I knew this was coming.
[gasps]
So there you have it.
She caused a malfunction
in our power supply system.
And as soon as everyone
escapes in a panic,
we find out everything's fine,
except we're locked out
of our own lab.
How amusing. Ah.
I mean, my,
that certainly is a tragedy.
[MALE STAFF 23B]
It's no use.
She's got control of
the whole security system.
[FEMALE STAFF 22A]
We need to do science!
It'll be fine. We have him.
He'll pull some magic,
I know it.
Administrative account
has been acquired.
Logging into the network.
After all, this is just
another game for him to win.
[REIKO gasps] My admin
rights got taken away!
Someone's shutting down
all my security measures!
Analyzing static
IP from access logs.
Checking for intrusion routes
and connected terminals.
[REIKO]
It has to be The Master!
Uh!
You learned this stuff
from me, Padawan.
Can't beat The Master
at his own game. Boom.
[JUNICHIRO]
Boom.
[YAMATO]
Huh? Wait! Why?
Why's he doing this?
'Sup?
What are you doing?
It's your fault.
You shouldn't try to stop me!
You said it yourself. I can't
let anyone boss me around!
Don't freak out.
Who said I'm here to stop you?
Huh?
Stomp me!
What?
Get over here and step on me!
Whatever you say!
I'll do my best!
Junichiro, open up! Come on!
It's not funny! Do it!
Open this gate now!
You must forgive me, Yamato,
but The Master
has been defeated!
[YAMATO]
Huh?
[JUNICHIRO]
She must've been training
in the hyperbolic time chamber,
'cause her martial arts
are super effective!
Hyperbolic?
I don't get the reference.
[YAMATO]
Oh right. I forgot.
This is Junichiro
we're dealing with.
Thank you, but why
are you doing this?
[JUNICHIRO]
It's obvious, isn't it?
'Cause siding with a bunch
of scientists is boring,
but siding
with you is super fun!
That's your reason?
Here I was being so serious.
[JUNICHIRO]
Barricading yourself in a lab?
C'mon, that's awesome.
I gotta get in on that action.
Okay, but it's not fair.
I had to do this so they
wouldn't take me away.
But it's like you get to
have fun wherever you go.
[JUNICHIRO] That's right.
Because I have YD,
so if I don't like it,
I can't do it.
Man. That sounds
like cheating.
It's not cheating. You can do
the same thing if you like.
And whether you do it
at school or not is up to you.
I thought I wanted
to work at this lab.
But maybe there's
something bigger than that.
Did Junichiro
convince her to come out?
What I want. What I want
is to live like The Master.
Oh yeah? Are you sure?
[REIKO] Yes, I'll be
just like The Master.
But I'll find my own fun.
At school, with everyone else.
And once I find it,
I'll never let go!
[REIKO] I won't fight you, Yomi.
I'm ready to go to school now.
Oh? And you're certain?
Yes.
You don't even need
Mr. Kagami to come along
and teach you?
[REIKO]
Mnn-mmm.
No. 'Cause his "fun" isn't at
school. It's here.
I'm ready. The Master's
already taught me
everything I need to know.
The rest is up to me.
And may I assume that
Mr. Kagami approves of this?
[JUNICHIRO]
My "fun" is here? I guess so.
Was working on
the Anywhere Door
with everyone really fun or not?
I never thought about it.
I've been waiting for this day!
[laughs]
I wish.
But when Reiko
stopped following my orders
to do what she wanted, I felt
something. Something familiar.
And then again,
when she took over the lab
because she didn't want to
go back to her old life
no matter what. There it was.
That spark.
That little light.
[KIRIKO]
Cut! Cut! Cut!
Hell yeah!
[laughs]
Nice to meet you.
You can call me Koutaro.
I look forward to
studying with you.
[JUNICHIRO]
Not just a spark, a crack too.
The sound of someone
emerging from their shell
a better, stronger character.
[TIM] I've got one little
question to trouble you with.
Are you still
masquerading as a teacher?
Don't act daft, we both
know what I'm talking about.
You do not truly yearn
to be an educator.
I mean, you've gotta
find teaching boring.
[JUNICHIRO]
It's not about teaching.
It's about creating
a new, better future.
Making dreams
and fantasy a reality,
like I've always yearned to do.
I get it now.
Thank you, Options.
I finally understand
what my role is as a teacher.
Are you ready
to take me back now?
[gasps]
Fair warning.
If I have my way,
I might make your
whole school obsolete.
What do you mean by that?
Let's call it
sudden inspiration.
You can do the same thing,
and whether you do it
at school or not is up to you.
I'm gonna make every
student want to quit school.
[KOYOMI]
Huh?
That's my new
educational policy.
I'll make them find something
so amazing in their lives
school will become meaningless.
Soon, they'll all
be infected with YD.
Yearning to reach their dream.
[KOYOMI]
Splendidly amusing!
That is precisely
the kind of teacher I want.
You so rarely disappoint!
You are now reinstated.
I trust you will proceed
with your full enthusiasm?
Heh. Of course!
I'm definitely going all-in!
Sorry Yamato.
It just wasn't meant to be.
Duty calls.
Oh, Junichiro.
Heh.
I should've seen this coming.
Go ahead, then.
But, listen, if I have another
emergency, I'm calling you--
[JUNICHIRO]
Thank you.
You've helped me
more than you know.
[JUNICHIRO chuckles]
Hope that science
stuff works out!
Just YD me
and then fly away, huh?
[JUNICHIRO] You had me dancing
in the palm of your hand
this whole time, didn't you?
You really love to meddle.
My! What do you mean?
All this mess just to
help me figure out
what it means
to be a teacher.
You sure are thorough.
You knew Yamato
wanted me to work at KEC,
so you fired me, confident that
I would go check out their lab.
Then you sent Reiko,
a would-be student,
who needed to learn
the concept of "fun."
Something I'm
an expert at, of course.
You even told Tim
I was working there
because every story
needs a villain.
Then I give one of
my famous lessons
and I'm back to being a teacher.
[KOYOMI] So you say, but you're
the one who got schooled.
Well, it's not like it matters.
Once I have my way, you might
want to fire me for real.
Hey, I'm home.
Not like anyone is here.
[JUNICHIRO]
Hey, welcome back.
"Welcome back"?
Wait, for real?
You're alive!
What the hell, bro?
You disappear for days
and couldn't bother
to return a call?
[JUNICHIRO]
Whoa, happy times, happy times!
You're a grownup!
I shouldn't have to
worry about you so much!
[sobs]
I'm sorry.
[SUZUNE] Okay then! I have
a test to study for tomorrow.
I wouldn't bother,
if I were you.
How rude!
You saying I'm stu--?
He's gone.
[KANAN grunting]
[KANAN] I know
I'm just a lunchtime DJ,
and that's not even really
a thing, but someday
people are gonna
hear this doofy anime voice
on national television!
And when You Red Pond
comes to Japan,
it's gonna be me
interviewing her live!
That's right, anime voice,
you and me are
going all the way!
It's so late!
What am I doing?
I have to study
for that test tomorrow!
[KANAN] I already know what
university I want to go to,
so it feels
like a waste studying
all this stuff I'll never use.
But, if I let my GPA slip,
I'll get stuck being
a dumb voice actor.
Huh? What is this about?
[school bell chimes]
[MALE TEACHER 24A]
Okay, begin your tests!
[FEMALE STUDENT 24A]
Ooh, I know this one!
[MALE STUDENT 24A]
Dude, it worked!
[KANAN]
Hmm?
[grunts]
[SUZUNE] What're you
trying to pull Junichiro?
[knock, knock]
Listen, we've got bad news!
It must be quite dire
if you've brought
teachers with you.
All the students are
getting perfect test scores
in every subject!
At this rate, tests and teachers
will both become obsolete!
You're referring to
Mr. Kagami's class, I presume?
I wish! No, it's every
class in the whole school!
And not just high school.
Our middle school
and grade schools, too!
--[KOYOMI] Oh my.
--[MAKINA] Look!
In other words,
Mr. Kagami has used this app
to extend his grimy paws
to the entire student body!
It's this
"Routine Buster" thing?
Hey kids, if you want to kick
all your exams to the curb,
then this
is the app for you!
That is adorable!
[MAKINA] That is not the issue!
Please, pay attention!
The Routine Buster
is an exam questions
prediction program
for all Icho students.
Enter the subject,
teacher name, and test date
to get the
questions and answers
faster than you can say
"studying sucks."
The program relies
on records of previous exams
as well as personal data
on the teachers
in order to create a prediction
with 90% accuracy.
We'll have to come up
with a new approach
when we write out our tests.
And teachers, I know
what you're thinking:
"we'll have to come up
with a new approach!"
but that only enhances
the richness
of the data in our system!
I've never been so
out-nerded in my life!
If I could
reach inside this phone,
I would wring your scrawny
little cartoon neck!
[KOYOMI] Mhm. You've thrown
down the gauntlet.
Well, I hired
you for a reason.
Let's see this educational
policy of yours in action.
You haven't seen
Mr. Kagami, have you?
[BOTH]
No.
[SUZUNE]
Oh, hey Kisaki.
Hello there.
Um. Have you seen
my brother around?
What, is he missing?
Please don't tell me
this's becoming a trend.
[KANAN] If you could turn your
attention to the clock tower,
you'll catch a special message
from the developer
of Routine Buster!
Oh, what now?
We'd better go watch.
[JUNICHIRO]
Students of Icho.
Are you studying
for your future?
Or has school
become nothing more
than a meaningless routine?
He's serious.
Did you see this?
Huh? He's on the clock tower?
What's he up to now?
Whoa. This is pretty
extreme, even for him.
[JUNICHIRO] Until today,
you had to study things
that had nothing
to do with your future,
because you need to
pass to the next grade,
or improve your GPA,
or maintain whatever
arbitrary standard they value
in the school system.
These things you study
you won't use.
You'll waste hours of
your life memorizing nonsense
that you'll forget
as soon as the test is over.
But now, with my app,
you can focus on your life.
On what matters to you.
But let me be frank.
The school takes no
responsibility for your future.
The only one
who can do that is you.
You're all free.
So find out what it is
you want in this world.
Make it happen
with your own two hands.
You don't need
an Anywhere Door.
You can go wherever
you please on your own!
And once you see
the world out there,
I hope you
find something so fun,
so life-changing, that you
don't even need school.
Is this guy out of his mind?
He's an embarrassment to our
profession. Let's shut him up!
[MALE TEACHER 24C]
Miss Momozono?
I understand your concern,
but it's far too late now.
You're not taking his side?
[STUDENTS cheering]
[MAKINA]
See?
[STUDENTS continue cheering]
[JUNICHIRO]
Now, engrave this in your heart.
You don't act because
you find something fun.
Rather, you discover
fun things through action.
This world is full
of treasures to find.
That's why you don't have
a second to spare
on things you don't love!
[STUDENTS cheering]
[KOYOMI] No one else will decide
what's important in their lives,
or tell them
what they need to do.
They will engage
only in what they enjoy.
A nation of
one hundred million YDs.
That's his vision
of an amusing Japan.
I've truly found
the right man for the job.
[KANAN, KIRIKO, KOUTARI]
Mr. Kagami!
--[KISAKI] Junichiro!
--[SEIJURO] Otaku teacher!
[SUZUNE]
Big bro!
[STUDENTS chanting]
Kagami! Kagami! Kagami!
[MADOKA]
Try as you might,
you just can't
put a price on that man.
[STUDENTS cheering]
[JUNICHIRO]
Well, this should be amusing.
Tomorrow's gonna be
even more enjoyable than today.
Okay. It's time
to start the lesson!