[JUNICHIRO]
I have YD.
You've say you've
never heard of it?
What?
I like wearing yukata on dates?
Or yummy dinners?
Wrong!
It's a debilitating
illness where you can
only do what you yearn to do.
[STUDENTS scream]
[MALE STUDENT A]
What the--?
You never know if your
car's gonna get in my way.
[SEIJURO, SUZUNE yell]
That's enough!
[BOTH gasp]
I found us the perfect
game to settle this!
You can't be serious right now.
[JUNICHIRO] Hey, if you don't
wanna play that's fine.
However, that will
count as your defeat.
In which case, I will be
releasing shameful photos
of lovely Miss Kanou
here to the internet!
[screams]
[SEIJURO growls]
Okay, punk. What're you
trying to pull here?
[JUNICHIRO] Nothing, but let
me introduce you to my team.
Icho Academy's best!
They made it into the top 4
during the last
prefectural tournament.
Right, guys?
[ALL]
Yes sir!
I put together a team
for you, too, of course.
[gasps]
[JUNICHIRO] The girls' soccer
club from East Shinmei High!
[ALL] It'll be tough, but we'll
give it our very best!
What the--? Are you
screwing around with me?
No, just looking for a fair
game of soccer, friend.
[growls]
You are so full of crap!
[MALE STUDENT A] How is
this supposed to be "fair"?
[FEMALE STUDENT A]
What a cheater!
Are you ready?
Let's get this show on the road.
[STUDENTS chatter]
Seeing as this is
a school matter,
I, Koyomi Hiiragi, shall be
the referee for this event.
[JUNICHIRO]
Huh? Okay.
As long as you're
familiar with the rules.
I didn't know you
were a soccer fan.
I read soccer manga if
that's what you're asking.
Of course! That's the only way!
Wait, for real?
[KIRIKO gasps]
[KOYOMI]
Ladies and gentlemen.
Let's begin the battle between
Mr. Kagami and Seijuro Nanami!
The winner of this soccer match
will enslave the loser
for the rest of his life!
Players, into positions!
[STUDENTS chatter]
[KAKITANI]
Mr. Kagami!
So, are you sure you can keep up
your end of the bargain here?
[JUNICHIRO] I said I
got you covered, right?
Everything's going
according to plan!
[SEIJURO] What "bargain?"
That dick must've bribed them.
Didn't make sense
for the soccer team
to cover him when he's only
been working here, like, a day.
You're a real piece of work.
Hmph. You know what?
Screw it. I don't care.
If you wanna play dirty,
I can do that too.
Time for the kick off!
[whistle blows]
[SOCCER PLAYERS grunting]
[SEIJURO yells]
[JUNICHIRO screams]
[gasps]
That looks bad!
[screams]
[JUNICHIRO]
Heh!
[JUNICHIRO grunts]
Ha! You mess with me?
That's what you get!
[SOCCER PLAYERS grunt]
Not telling you
how to do your job,
but I think that was a foul!
Bravo, nice tackle!
[SUZUNE groans] I don't know
what manga she's been reading,
but this does not bode well.
[SOCCER PLAYERS grunt]
[whistle blows]
That's one point! Team Kagami!
--[STUDENTS cheer]
--[SEIJURO gasps]
[SUZUNE]
Oh, yay!
I guess it worked out!
[JUNICHIRO] If you wanna
be my slave that bad,
you can just forfeit.
Ha!
[growls]
[whistle blows]
[SOCCER PLAYERS grunting]
[JUNICHIRO]
Over here!
[SEIJURO yells]
[JUNICHIRO grunts]
[JUNICHIRO groans]
Hey, you like cheating,
so let's keep it up.
You'll be eating out of
a tube when I'm done.
[whistle blows]
[KOYOMI]
Goal!
[MALE SOCCER PLAYER H]
Nice shot!
[grunts]
[JUNICHIRO]
Wow, two goals already.
Y'know, Cyborg. You might want
to get your AI unit checked.
[growls]
Oh yeah?!
Seijuro, stop it!
I don't know what kind of
deal you've got going on,
but we're trying to play a
proper game of soccer here.
Could you concentrate on the
game for five lousy minutes?
[AKO]
We want to win, okay?
[gasps]
[SEIJURO] Dammit.
"Concentrate on the game?"
I don't even know how
to dribble the damn ball!
[SOCCER PLAYERS grunting]
--[whistle blows]
--[KOYOMI] Goal!
[STUDENTS cheer]
Alright!
[JUNICHIRO]
Cool!
Now, we've got three! Heh!
[growls]
You're dead!
Seijuro, stop!
Go to hell!
--[whistle blows]
--[KOYOMI] That's enough!
Save that attitude for later.
Because it's half time!
[MALE SOCCER TEAM chatters]
[JUNICHIRO grunts]
For the MVP.
Yeah, I wish. Thanks.
If you can keep this up,
the match'll be a real cinch!
[FEMALE SOCCER TEAM sighs]
[YUI]
Seijuro.
[SEIJURO grunts]
I'm done with this mess!
It's all BS anyway!
It's not like I can
beat their best players
with a bunch of chicks,
so the whole thing is
busted from the start!
[FEMALE SOCCER TEAM gasps]
Fine. You wanna play soccer?
Go ahead, but if some cheating
otaku thinks I'm gonna roll
with his broken-ass game,
he can screw himself!
Would you calm down?
Finally getting interesting.
Sure took him long enough.
You know what's next.
That's right!
Time to start the lesson. Heh!
[MALE TEACHER 06A]
So, as an overview,
the Taika Reforms began at the
end of the Asuka era, in 645 AD.
[phone buzzes]
Many political changes were
made and the palace was...
[MINAKO]
Huh? From Mr. Kagami?
[gasps]
[MINAKO]
What?
[SEIJURO]
Huh? What do you want?
If it's about the slave thing,
then we can settle
this with our fists,
or you can get out
of my damn way.
I'll pass, thank you.
You're just a boring,
one-off villain.
There's no point in
having a slave like you.
You are smarter than
you look, though.
Some would call you
a coward for quitting.
But not me, if you've made
it this far in life,
someone raised you right.
Your dear old dad, I'm sure.
[gasps, growls]
[gasping]
[whistle blows]
I think it's time to
start the second half.
[chuckles]
[grunts]
All right, listen up!
I'm playing for real now,
so let's do this.
[JUNICHIRO]
Heh!
[STUDENTS cheer]
[SOCCER PLAYERS shout]
[SOCCER PLAYERS grunting]
[whistle blows]
[SEIJURO growls] I can
still turn this around!
[SOCCER PLAYERS grunting]
[KAKITANI]
Go! Go!
[SOCCER PLAYERS grunting]
--Here!
--[SEIJURO grunts]
[SOCCER PLAYERS grunting]
And it's in!
Are you sure this is
what you want, teach?
[FEMALE SOCCER PLAYER A sobs]
[KAKITANI] I'm kinda
starting to feel like a bully.
Just give it some time.
Cyborg's about to go
super saiyan on us.
[JUNICHIRO]
And the rule is, of course.
He can't transform
until he's really angry.
[panting]
I think we're done for.
It's not looking great.
We can score one, can't we?
[SEIJURO] I really hate
to lay into the girls
when I'm tripping over
my own damn feet,
but we are seriously
outclassed here.
This sucks!
There's gotta be
something I can do!
[MINAKO]
Hey, you dope!
[gasps]
Why are you
wasting your time
trying to play soccer
the normal way?
That's dumb!
Think back for a second.
Remember your training!
--[SUZUNE] Huh?
--Miss Kanou!
[JUNICHIRO] Ooh, good line.
Spoken like a true voice actor.
Training?
[SEIJURO]
Hmm...
Wait, I get it!
[SEIJURO] I'll wipe the
floor with those punks.
Just you wait and see!
That's right. It's time
for a comeback!
[SOCCER PLAYERS grunting]
'Kay! Here!
Right! Cool!
[KAKITANI]
Well, that's something.
'Least their passes
are getting through.
They were taking some pretty
risky shots in the first half.
[KAKITANI]
Just passing the ball around
in their defensive zone won't
get them anywhere, though.
They're still behind.
You think they just
gave up on winning?
Not that I could blame them.
Okay, I take it back,
but that's one heck
of a desperate pass.
I mean, for starters, there's
not even anyone there.
[gasps]
[KAKITANI] I don't know what
they were shooting for.
You gotta defend
the goal, hurry!
Huh? I really don't think
they're gonna make it.
[KAKITANI gasps]
[SEIJURO yells]
[KAKITANI yells]
[gasps, yelps]
[SEIJURO shouts]
[whistle blows]
[KOYOMI]
Goal!
That's my kind of soccer!
[murmuring]
What was that? He was
like a freight train!
It's called "kick and rush."
Huh?
It may seem a little crazy,
kicking a ball all the way from
the other end of the field.
But then a powerful
forward follows up on it.
[SEIJURO grunting]
[JUNICHIRO] In the world
of soccer video games,
there is no greater strategy.
[KAKITANI]
Wait, what?
[JUNICHIRO] Of course, it
doesn't come up much in reality.
Seeing as it requires someone to
run even faster than the ball.
I know what you're thinking.
It doesn't seem
humanly possible, right?
[JUNICHIRO] But for a
super-powered cyborg
like our friend here,
it's all in a day's work.
[FEMALE SOCCER TEAM]
All right, you did it!
Yeah!
[JUNICHIRO] I knew you
were something special
the moment I saw you!
I mean, you did send a
car flying, after all.
[SOCCER PLAYERS grunting]
--[whistle blows]
--[KOYOMI] Goal!
[SOCCER PLAYERS grunting]
--[whistle blows]
--[KOYOMI] Goal number three!
[STUDENTS cheer]
[SEIJURO yells]
--[cheering]
--[KOYOMI] Four!
[SEIJURO yells]
--[whislte blows]
--[KOYOMI] Five!
[STUDENTS cheer]
That's crazy!
No kidding!
[Now it's tied.
The second half
has barely started
and they've caught up already!
Okay, they took us by surprise,
but we gotta figure this out
before it gets even worse.
It's the same thing every time,
so surely we can stop it.
[JUNICHIRO] You'd think so,
but it's not so simple.
[KAKITANI]
What do you mean?
[JUNICHIRO]
Or rather, it is that simple.
It's so effective and
so straightforward
that they ban the tactic
in PVP tournaments.
Yeah, but you're only
talking about video games.
There's no reason
why real players
have to fall for that crap!
We're running out of time!
We gotta defend that goal,
even if it kills us!
After that, we rally!
[MALE SOCCER TEAM]
Yeah!
[JUNICHIRO] You really
are clueless, aren't you?
Don't look down on
video game characters.
They don't have to
play by our rules.
They can break bricks
with their fist
and double jump and
do all sorts of things.
[MALE SOCCER PLAYER I]
Here he comes!
Okay, defend the goal!
[JUNICHIRO]
And if they can run faster
than a kicked soccer ball,
they don't care about defense,
or the goalie or any of that.
Physics don't apply to them.
[yelling]
[JUNICHIRO] This guy's got
the star. He's invincible.
He's gonna kick your logic
and your butts to the curb.
[SOCCER PLAYERS grunting]
[yelling]
--[whistle blows]
--[KOYOMI] Goal!
[cheering]
He did it!
[whistle blowing]
And that's the end of
the game, everyone.
Team Nanami wins six to five!
--[AYAKA] I can't believe it!
--[FEMALE SOCCER PLAYERS cheer]
Hell yeah!
[KIRIKO]
That's not good.
[SUZUNE]
My brother the slave.
Nope. Not cool.
[SEIJURO]
Hey, slave!
You tried to cheat me out of the
win and now you're gonna pay
for the rest of
your miserable, otaku life.
I guess so. Sure sucks to be me!
[grunts]
Hey smartass. I wasn't
making a damn joke.
If you don't wipe that
smile off your face,
I'm gonna kick your teeth in!
[YUI]
Seijuro!
Huh?
That was like a
dream come true!
Thanks for helping us put
those guys in their place!
You were super
awesome back there!
[YUI] Mr.Kagami told us
we could beat them easy
with a little help from you.
Jeez, he wasn't kidding!
Huh?
Run that by me again?
I guess it was supposed
to be a surprise,
but he said you'd be
really great at soccer
and he needed our help
to set up a game for you.
He was really going
out on a limb to help
and it sounded like fun,
so I thought "why not?"
Wait a sec!
I saw her at work the other day,
talking to Mr. Kagami!
[JUNICHIRO] I'll give you
a real show! And trust me.
You won't want to
miss these shots!
Oh, I'll be watching closely.
[JUNICHIRO] Good,
I'm so happy to hear that.
[KIRIKO]
Then that means.
It's no contest who's gonna
win this thing but I promise,
it will blow your mind!
You jerk! Stop flirting!
He wasn't bragging.
He was just talking
about Seijuro.
Hey! You gonna
explain this, or what?
[MALE SOCCER PLAYER E]
Seijuro!
Dude, that was crazy cool!
Even though you dominated us,
that was the most fun
I've had in a while!
I dunno how you did that,
but it was awesome!
What's going on?
[KAKITANI]
Welcome to the team!
You're totally gonna
be our new star player!
Hold on a second.
I don't get any of this.
[KAKITANI]
My bad.
We thought you were in on it.
Mr. Kagami said he
was gonna show us
a player straight
out of a video game.
All we had to do
was play a match.
[gasps]
[KAKITANI] I thought he was full
of it at first, so I said no.
[KAKITANI] But then he
waited outside my house
all night with these
sad puppy eyes.
I felt bad for him,
so I gave in.
[SUZUNE]
Ah-ha!
[KIRIKO]
I hope he explodes!
[KIRIKO sobs]
Huh? Okay?
Not sure I even want to
know that that was about.
[SUZUNE]
Now it makes sense!
I thought he was gone all night
'cause he was being weird,
but I guess not.
Well, anyway, the game
turned out great
and we've got an
awesome new player!
[MALE SOCCER PLAYER G]
That's what I'm saying!
[MALE SOCCER PLAYER
F]We're gonna make nationals
this year for sure!
[KAKITANI]
Thanks man.
We've been waiting
for someone like you.
Should be fun.
Huh?
[JUNICHIRO]
I'll spell it out.
These guys want to
play soccer with you.
Sounds like a good time to me.
[gasps]
It's not like
I don't want to join,
but I've never even
played before today.
[KAKITANI] Aw, who cares!
You're a natural athlete
and you're already
good enough to beat us,
so I think you'll be fine.
Let's kick some
butt together, okay?
[gasps]
[TEAMMATE A] Hey, you know where
I think Seijuro should play?
[TEAMMATE B]
The batting cages. Alone.
[SEIJURO'S FATHER]
One day, you'll be all alone,
with nothing left but regret.
[SEIJURO grunts]
[JUNICHIRO]
You're not alone anymore.
[chuckles]
[gasps]
[SUZUNE] Aw, that's nice.
He was trying to put Seijuro
back on track by
getting him into soccer!
[JUNICHIRO]
Huh?
Does that sound like me at all?
No, this is like
a life Sim game
where I get to raise
a cyborg monster
instead of some boring pet!
--[SUZUNE] Are you kidding me?
--[KIRIKO] Huh?
Your technology could still
use a few modifications.
But, don't worry.
This mad scientist
is on top of things.
We'll have you wreaking
even more havoc in no time!
Damn it.
You're the one who's
supposed to be the slave!
[JUNICHIRO]
Anyway, thanks.
That was a pretty good show.
I yearned to see
something exciting
and with a little help
from you, it totally happened.
That's all there is to it.
"Something exciting?"
Are you serious?
I'm an otaku.
Seeing a video game
character come to life
was a big deal for me.
So yeah, I'm dead serious.
Don't you think it was fun?
[SEIJURO] All that trouble.
Just to get a laugh out of this?
[SEIJURO'S FATHER] Someone like
that will be a good friend,
I'm sure, but I'm afraid they'll
probably be an idiot, too.
[SEIJURO'S FATHER] Living your
life that way will alienate you.
One day, you'll be all alone,
with nothing left but regret.
But if it really means
that much to you,
if you have to follow that
path no matter what,
maybe someday
someone will understand.
Instead of being pushed away,
that person may be excited
to see where life takes you.
And to share it with you.
Someone like that will
be a good friend, I'm sure,
but I'm afraid they'll
probably be an idiot, too.
[SEIJURO]
He wanted me to play soccer,
just so he could
see something crazy.
Even when I got mad
and attacked him,
he just stuck to the
plan and watched.
Heh! You win, otaku teacher,
I admit defeat.
[JUNICHIRO]
Hm?
Okay, this is getting weird.
So, according to our
little agreement,
I'm your loyal slave
and you get to do
whatever the hell
you want with me.
I may have won the game,
but I'm the one who got played.
[chuckles]
Don't ever change, Cyborg.
Hold on--!
And thus ends another lesson.
[MINAKO]
Seijuro!
Miss Kanou!
That was straight up amazing!
[SEIJURO] He only does
what he yearns to do.
That's kinda cool, huh.
Ha! Even I'm getting carried
away by this guy's style.
Damn it.
I can't blame you
for falling in love.
Huh? Where did
you get that from?
Whoa, wait! Ah!
No, you don't have to choke me,
I'm saying it's okay, I approve!
[SEIJURO grunting]
All in a day's
work for you, huh?
[JUNICHIRO] So you say,
but I was dancing to
your tune the entire time,
wasn't I?
Well?
Were you sufficiently amused?
Yes. Quite thoroughly.
[SEIJURO grunting]
[MINAKO] I'll choke some
common sense into you!
[chuckles]
[KOYOMI] I knew inviting
you here was a good idea.
Let us hope this is only the
beginning of a long career.
[SEIJURO grunts]
[MINAKO] I hope you like
sleeper holds, buddy,
'cause I can keep
this up all day!
[SEIJURO grunts]
[SUZUNE]
Suzune here!
You didn't forget me, did you?
I'm the adorable little sister!
Anyway, Seijuro's on our side
now, so life's 100% less scary!
The next problem
student is Kanan Chinami.
She's the prettiest
girl in the school,
but nobody's ever
heard her voice
'cause she only talks
with text messages!
Is that bonkers or what?
Period seven,
"A Beautiful Girl's Secret."
I heard a rumor that
she actually sounds
just like an anime character!
Uh-oh!
You better not make her
say anything weird, bro!