Hey! Don't change that channel!
You don't wanna miss
a second of this one!
An heiress who can
assess a man's value
has her eyes on yours truly.
Today's lesson will be about
discovering your "self-worth."
All teachers are looking
for diamonds in the rough,
and I, Junichiro Kagami,
the Ultimate Otaku Teacher,
always find them first!
[MADOKA] My, my.
Nothing but pocket change.
Is there really no
man worth his salt?
I've seen more dollar signs
between the sofa cushions.
Hmm...
Although, I guess
that's to be expected.
When supply is high,
demand will be low.
[SOCCER PLAYER  A]
I can't hear you!
[SOCCER PLAYERS]
Yeah!
[MALE ICHO SOCCER PLAYERS]
One, two! One, two! Fight on!
Fight on! One, two...
[JUNICHIRO groans]
--[stomach growls]
--[groaning continues]
[sighs]
[JUNICHIRO] Three weeks ago,
I managed to convince Suzune
to start giving me lunch money
instead of making me
brown bag every day.
Little does she know,
I've actually been
saving the cash
and getting by on just water.
[chuckles]
[JUNICHIRO]
But that ends today,
because I've finally
saved up enough money
to snag me a copy
of Battle World 3!
[MUSCLE CLUB LEADER]
Yo! You can't do me like that!
[JUNICHIRO]
Hm?
[MADOKA]
Complain all you like,
but you're not
getting another cent.
Dude, what?
But that's cutting the Muscle
Adventure Club's budget by,
like, ninety percent
or something, right?
Well I'm impressed.
I didn't know you could do
math like that in your head!
Of course, it doesn't
change the fact
that you yourself are only
worth six-fifty, little boy!
[gasps]
What?
'Kay, gang, can I
help who's next?
Bro, she ain't serious
with this, right?
Well that was nice.
Ever heard of tact, Kuramochi?
Hey, I wasn't trying to be ugly.
I was just giving
them their flat rate.
Don't be so stuffy!
What? "Stuffy?" "Flat rate?"
[JUNICHIRO]
Hey, Twin-Tails weirdo!
Great. What are you doing here?
I work here. Who's she?
[MAKINA grunts]
[MAKINA]
Her name's Madoka Kuramochi.
She has a talent for
determining the net worth
of anything she
looks at on the fly.
That includes people,
just so you know.
Sounds like a big
shot naming a bounty.
She's been a big help
to the student council.
It may seem a little cold,
but she's never given out a
budget that's gone to waste.
Despite only being
in her first year,
she's already our
full-time accountant.
And one day she'll inherit
her family's company.
She's hacked.
There's no way to have such high
character stats without cheats.
Well... I don't think that
means her life is easy.
[gasps] Wait, you only
teach part-time.
If you don't have a class, why
are you just hanging around?
Oh, uh...
Actually, I was hoping I could
find someone to buy me lunch.
[stomach growls]
You bum!
You can't extort your students
into getting food for you!
No way! Not on my watch!
Mr. Kagami!
Whoa! Deep breaths!
[gasps]
[MADOKA]
What'd she say?
You call yourself
a teacher?
Leave!
[yelps]
[MAKINA] You can
buy your own lunches!
[MADOKA]
So he's Junichiro Kagami.
Interesting.
[JUNICHIRO]
Da na na na!
The wait is over!
Man, it sure feels
satisfying to buy something
with my hard-earned money!
[laughing]
All right!
[JUNICHIRO]
Heh? Oh, cool, a flea market.
Wonder if there's anything
worth my spare change?
[JUNICHIRO]
Huh?
[gasps]
Whoa!
Sergeant Saunders in Close
Combat Mode is a must buy!
You may consider this
one purchased, my man!
[MERCHANT]
Nice choice!
[MADOKA]
Now, let's not be hasty!
You don't mind if I give this
doll a once over, do you?
I, uh, suppose that's
not a problem.
She's so cute!
What a shame.
She comes at such an
unreasonably high price.
Nuh-uh, it's a steal.
That's a limited edition--
--[MADOKA] Up!
--[gasps]
She just took her innocence!
Huh?
Well, sir.
She's looking a tad rough
right around the lady parts.
Uh-uh...
How can this be?
[JUNICHIRO]
Thanks for catching that.
I'd have hated buying
something that was damaged.
Plus, that guy was
so embarrassed,
he gave me a better discount.
[MADOKA]
It wasn't a big deal.
No, I owe you.
How can I pay you back?
Let's see.
I suppose if you're offering,
today is my sixteenth birthday.
Really? You don't say.
Well, in that case,
if there's something I
can give you, it's yours.
[MADOKA]
Hmm...
Huh?
The only thing
I want is you.
Huh?
Way to make it weird.
Ugh. I'm out.
Whoa! Stop right there!
[JUNICHIRO grunts]
Are you trying to
get away from me?
[grunts]
--[MADOKA gasps]
--[JUNICHIRO laughs]
You think people
would know by now,
no one can catch
me in Akihabara!
Get back here!
[JUNISHIRO chuckles]
[MADOKA]
Stop running!
[JUNICHIRO]
Yeah, right!
[MADOKA pants]
[JUNICHIRO pants]
[MADOKA breathes heavily]
[JUNICHIRO]
Heh? Hmm...
Finally lost her.
That girl sure had
an odd request.
What would she want me for?
[MUSCLE CLUB LEADER]
Found you, prima dona!
[MUSCLE CLUB MEMBER A]
We need to talk!
[MUSCLE CLUB MEMBER B]
Yeah, what he said!
[JUNICHIRO]
Not good.
[MUSCLE CLUB LEADER]
Thanks to you, we can't afford
protein shakes or
haircuts no more.
And you're gonna pay for that.
Wow, turned a phrase.
Unfortunately, that's not
nearly enough to help you
with your monetary concerns.
See, it's your bad attitude
that made your price low.
[growls]
[MADOKA gasps]
[MUSCLE CLUB LEADER]
You got an awful big mouth
for someone so small.
So I'm gonna shut it!
[gasps]
[yells]
[JUNICHIRO grunts]
[gasps]
[MUSCLE CLUB LEADER]
What the hell is this?
--[JUNICHIRO grunts]
--[MADOKA whimpers]
Heh.
[OTAKU A gasps]
Mitsuki-chan!
Where art thou?
[gasps]
Huh?
We saw on social media a
famous cosplayer was gonna be
doing a photoshoot in
this creepy back alley!
That is why
you're here, isn't it?
No, we're here for...
What?
They're gone!
[MUSCLE CLUB MEMBER B]
Where'd they go?
[BOTH pant]
Only took the
otaku-razzi
three minutes to get there
after I made that post.
I guess they bring new meaning
to the phrase "gotta go fast!"
Still cut it close, though.
I guess I owe you now
after that save--
[screams]
Oh! My copy of Battle World 3
is in a million pieces now!
[MADOKA]
Is it really worth crying over?
Of course!
This game is made by KMC,
the fastest-growing video
game developer in Japan
because they're known for
going against the grain!
FPS games are mostly
from Western companies.
KMC is the only
Japanese publisher
to have any significance
in that genre!
And I skipped lunch
for fifteen days
just to be able to
support their noble cause!
[sobs]
I get it, okay?
Here!
[JUNICHIRO gasps] A new
copy of Battle World 3!
Uh. Why do you
have this?
[MADOKA]
Because KMC
just happens to be
my family's company!
[gasps]
[JUNICHIRO]
What?!
You're telling me that's
the family business
you're supposed to inherit?
[MADOKA] Sure is.
Remember when I told
you it was my birthday?
My family has a tradition.
When a child reaches sixteen,
he or she must find a partner
who will help support them
so they can take over
the business together.
[gasps]
Well? It's my turn today,
and I'd heard an
awful lot about you.
It didn't really hit me
until I saw you in person,
but... now I know.
Yeah?
You are the only one for me!
If I can have you by my side,
then there's nothing
we can't accomplish!
Just think! We could
make video games
that the whole world
would want to play!
[grunts]
What d'you say?
I know it's sudden, but I'm
not such a bad catch, am I?
[grunts]
I'm sorry, but you barely
know anything about me.
And getting married
without building up
any relationship points would
lead us both to the bad ending.
Besides, if I'm not mistaken,
your company's up
in the Hills, right?
No way I could live in
such an uptight place.
I'd probably suffocate within
thirty seconds of being there.
See ya later!
[grunts]
[CROWD cheers]
[GATES]
Hmph.
[CROWD cheers]
[ANNOUNCER]
You saw it coming, folks!
He has overpowered his opponents
and claimed the championship
title for the third
year in a row!
Your winner is Hell Gates!
[BODYGU ARD] It seems the
situation has come to a head.
I see.
I suppose I have no choice but
to handle it myself, then.
Get the jet ready.
We'll depart as soon as I
finish my own preparations.
[MALE BODYGUARD 14A]
Yes sir.
[chuckles]
[GATES]
Just you wait.
[doorbell rings]
[SUZUNE]
Coming!
Huh? What the--?
Uh... Hey, bro! Come here!
Look at this.
[JUNICHIRO grunts]
I see it. Hm?
It's not my birthday, right?
Hi!
[JUNICHIRO gasps]
How are you, darlin'?
Time for a free
housewife sample!
[gasps]
You know what? You were right!
We don't know enough
about each other!
So, I decided to come
and spend the night!
That is not going to help!
[SUZUNE]
Didn't you get your fill of
overnight guests
last week, bro?
[JUNICHIRO]
Otaku Sense tingling!
So what's your excuse
for this one?
Who is this girl and why does
she want to jump your bones?
Well, uh.
I can't believe he didn't
tell you! I'm his fiancé.
We're gonna make the biggest
video game company
ever together!
[JUNICHIRO gasps]
What?
Come on.
[SUZUNE growls]
Along the way,
we're gonna bring eleven
bundles of joy into the world!
Then our babies will sign on
with a soccer team like Namba
Osaka and compete
in championships!
They're gonna make their mama
and papa so proud of them!
[JUNICHIRO]
Slow down!
Listen. Suzune,
allow me to explain.
And I figured, if we
want to stand a chance
at making our dreams come true,
we'll have to get started early!
[JUNICHIRO] Will you please
stop talking already?
[SUZUNE] I guess it'll
be okay for one night.
[SUZUNE] I dunno where
she got this crazy idea,
but that much time with my bro
should be a sufficient
reality check.
However, you'll sleep
in my room.
I'm the alpha dog here,
so you'll follow my rules.
But of course!
Till you're done in
like Old Yeller,
I am happy to oblige,
new sister!
So go ahead and leave
all of today's chores
and what not to me!
Fine. Hmph.
[SUZUNE]
You sure talk a big game,
but let's see you back it up.
[JUNICHIRO ]
You're really giving her
free reign of the house?
[SUZUNE]
Why not?
If she's such an eager beaver
to clean, I'll let her.
I'm totally down with
taking a day off.
If you say so.
[MADOKA]
Dinner's ready!
Huh?
[JUNICHIRO, SUZUNE gasp]
[MADOKA] Tonight's menu for
the athletic younger sister,
includes a high protein,
low fat feast!
And for our resident otaku,
a variety of dishes cultivated
from some of his all-time,
favorite shows!
No way, this is
real manga meat!
And the spaghetti
and eggs 'n toast
are from some of the best anime!
Yeah, great.
It looks good,
but how's it taste?
[gasps]
This food is incredible!
I can't believe you
actually made all of it!
Thank you.
[chuckles]
What I meant to say is
"it's not that good,"
so don't get any ideas!
Here, I have a special
treat for you, darlin'.
Cheese toast from the alps!
Now say, "ah."
Ah!
[chuckles]
[sighs]
Delicious and stretchy,
just like in the show!
That's not all! Open!
[JUNICHIRO]
Yummy dinner!
[MADOKA] What did you think?
Was my cooking to your liking?
You'd better believe it was!
Best meal ever!
Well in that case. Got a pen?
Huh? For what?
[JUNICHIRO gasps]
Oh, no!
Now, now,
don't be so coy!
You know full well
why I came over.
I'm here to prove how
valuable I am to you.
Now admit it and
we can get married!
[JUNICHIRO gasps]
I hate to say this,
but I'm impressed.
Despite being younger than me,
you're a much better cook.
That's totally unfair.
Also...
Just look at this place,
it's spotless!
Your housekeeping
skills are top notch.
Thanks. But honestly,
this was a slice a pie.
My family's trained me for
much worse than this place!
Whoa.
By the way, I went ahead and
drew a bath for ya, Darling.
Uh, thanks?
--[SUZUNE growls]
--[MADOKA gasps]
--You are coming with me!
--[MADOKA] What's the matter?
I'm just showing hospitality!
[yelps]
[MADOKA] Why'd you yank
me away like that?
Don't tell me
you've never heard,
"absence makes the
heart grow fonder"?
Take a breather.
I'll be right here.
There's no way
she can get by me.
[JUNICHIRO]
Thanks, sis.
[JUNICHIRO] I wonder what
Miss Money Bags is up to?
I get it. She likes me.
But why be so forward
about all this?
And now that I
think about it,
why would the heiress to a video
game company need to be
master level in things like
cooking and cleaning?
Something's not adding up.
[gasps]
[MADOKA]
Hey, honey!
Want me to wash your back?
What I want is to know
how you got in here!
Oh, c'mon now.
I scaled down the balcony,
jumped into the family room,
and snuck in through
a side window!
I had to 'cause your sister
locked her bedroom door.
[JUNICHIRO]
You should've taken the hint!
We have to get to
know each other
and what better way than
for us to just bare all?
Unbelievable.
[MADOKA]
16's legal here.
And that means I'm
officially on the market.
Wanna buy?
[sighs]
[JUNICHIRO] In the interest
of learning about each other.
tell me why you're in such
a rush to get married.
Uh... I haven't a clue
what you're talking about.
[JUNICHIRO]
I've never seen anything like
your instant appraisals.
They're thorough and exact,
and it's worked very well here
because you've nailed
my interests to a T.
So you must know I wouldn't like
the straightforward approach,
but you're shooting
for it all the same.
[sighs]
[MADOKA]
I have a dream.
One day, I want to marry
someone I truly love.
Then he and I will make
a video game together
the whole world will play.
To do that, I would
give up everything.
You would?
But why pick someone like me?
[door clatters]
Hey. I thought I heard voices.
[gasps]
[SUZUNE screams]
[JUNICHIRO grunts]
Repent, sinner!
[JUNICHIRO] Why is
this happening to me?
Then again, I really
should have seen it coming.
That's enough funny
business for one night.
Dog in the manger. I get it.
You love your brother,
but come on.
You don't have to be stingy!
Of course we love
each other. We're family.
[MADOKA] Yeah, I can see that
by looking at your desk.
Huh?
[MADOKA] That's an awful
sweet photo of you kids.
It must mean a lot
to you to have it out
where everyone can see.
[SUZUNE gasps]
[MADOKA]
It's fine.
I can understand why you're
so protective of him.
It's almost like he can
see right through me.
I've never met anyone like
him in all my life...
[SUZUNE]
No surprise there.
He's pretty weird.
Ever since I was a little kid,
whenever something
is bothering me,
he always sticks his
nose in and handles it
before I can think of
asking him for help.
[sighs]
[SUZUNE]
My whole life's been like that.
[MADOKA giggles]
Y'know, you're lucky.
I think that goes to show how
much he really cares for you.
Huh?
To him, your happiness
is priceless.
Kind of makes me jealous.
[SUZUNE]
What do you mean?
[MADOKA]
Never mind.
It's not worth explainin'.
[MADOKA]
Forget I said anything.
[typing]
Alright. I've got admin access.
That's why. In order to do that,
I would give up everything.
[JUNICHIRO]
What would inspire her
to say something like that?
[clicking]
[JUNICHIRO]
Not this.
Not here either.
[clicking]
[gasps]
Here we go.
[clicking]
No way! Dude! You're kidding me!
[MALE CUSTOMER B]
Not a joke, man.
He's going for
the knife-only win.
He hasn't fired a single
shot this entire time!
[MALE CUSTOMER C] I didn't
think that was even possible!
He's playing on the highest
difficulty setting, too!
It's unreal!
[FEMALE CUSTOMER A] It's like
he knows where the enemies
are going to spawn
before the game loads them!
[MALE CUSTOMER B]
This is freakin' incredible!
He's actually gonna do it!
Who is this guy?
[chuckles]
[MADOKA sighs]
[JUNICHIRO] The world's
largest video game company,
is Activision-Frigate.
Total corporate
stock value: two-trillion.
Mr. Kagami.
[JUNICHIRO]
Hope you don't mind,
but I went ahead and did some
research on your company.
If they opted for
a buyout. That'd be it.
KMC's only worth ten-billion,
so there's no choice, is there?
That why you've been in
such a rush to get married?
I guess when it comes to you,
I can't hide anything, can I?
Ah, well.
No point in beating
around the bush.
There's actually a secret
condition to that agreement.
It involves me.
In order for our employees
to remain on staff
after the big buy out,
I have to take the hand of the
chief executive
officer in matrimony.
[gasps]
But if I decline his proposal,
they'll fire every one
of our workers without
a second thought.
This is exactly what my parents
were getting ready for when they
trained me in housekeepin'.
So, no, I don't have any
choice in the matter.
Now do you see?
That's why...
I literally know
how much I'm worth.
Sorry I kept this from you.
I didn't want you to have
any reason to doubt my
feelings were true.
Because I really would
like to marry you.
Call me a coward.
[MADOKA] I figured if
I had you by my side.
I could make all my
dreams come true.
But sometimes you've
got to wake up, right?
[MADOKA gasps]
Don't act like you
know everything, Money Bags.
I'm not letting you
go out on that note.
[MADOKA]
Uh... Huh?
Heh. The survival of a video
game company relies solely
on an inter-corporate
political marriage?
They make summer blockbusters
about that kind of
crazy situation.
And yet, the plot has
only begun to thicken!
[MADOKA] Hey, all,
this is Madoka Kuramochi!
I've never met anyone
like Mr. Kagami before.
That's why he's so attractive.
Next episode,
genius programmer
Hell Gates arrives!
Wait, what's he doing here?
Mr. Kagami, you can't
make a promise like that!
You had better have a plan!
Period Fifteen,
"The Fiancé is a Game King."
You need to take
this seriously!
But I hope you win.
I really don't want to marry
someone I don't love.