[JUNICHIRO]
I have YD.
You say you've
never heard of it?
What?
I like wearing
yukata on dates?
Or yummy dinners?
Wrong!
It's a debilitating
illness where you
can only do what
you yearn to do.
You're gonna be a teacher,
starting tomorrow.
[JUNICHIRO]
The other kids.
Why are they picking on you?
Just wondering
why you like picking
on Minako Kanou so much.
[MIHO]
We don't!
We have no idea what
you're talking about, sir!
Isn't that right, girls?
I said I wanted to get through
this on my own didn't I?
[JUNICHIRO] Being a hero
may be a lonely fight,
but that doesn't mean
you have to do it alone.
[laughs]
[JUNICHIRO gaspss]
No.
No!
[JUNICHIRO whimpers] My anime
blog dropped to number 2?!
[JUNICHIRO screams]
[JUNICHIRO] This is because
of that stupid teaching job!
Can't I just screw
around online all day?
Work is for losers!
Reposting anime news stories
is all that matters in life!
[sighs]
[YUKINO]
Mr. Kagami?
Mr. Kagami!
Wake up!
[clattering]
[JUNICHIRO]
Huh?
[YUKINO]
Are you listening?
--[STUDENTS chatter]
--[JUNICHIRO] Wha--?
Please, sir. Stop groaning
and teach the class.
[JUNICHIRO]
Okay.
Uhm.
[STUDENTS murmur]
[JUNICHIRO sighing]
[MIHO, YOKO, KEIKO giggle]
[JUNICHIRO grunts]
Why is chalk so heavy?
[groaning]
[sighs] I just don't
want to do it enough.
[chattering continues]
[MINAKO giggles]
[JUNICHIRO] Curse this
crippling infirmary of mine.
[YUKINO growls]
[school bells ring]
[JUNICHIRO sighs] Somehow I
made it through another day,
but this really is
cruelty to otaku.
Why can't the world
understand my plight?
[MIHO]
We are so sorry, Minako.
--[YOKO] Yeah, like, seriously.
--[KEIKO] We were awful to you.
[MINAKO]
Whatever. I'm over it.
[JUNICHIRO]
Hm.
[JUNICHIRO chuckles]
[JUNICHIRO gasps]
[CROWD chatters]
[SUZUNE] We haven't spent a
Sunday together in a while.
--It's nice to go out.
--[JUNICHIRO chuckles]
[JUNICHIRO] I'd have more
time for you, dear sister,
if you hadn't made me get
that abhorrent teaching job.
[JUNICHIRO cheers]
[JUNICHIRO] It's such a
pity how my busy schedule
leaves me with no free time,
so I'm forced to scramble
to catch up on
chores all weekend!
But if you let me quit,
then we can have fun
like this all the time!
That's totally not true.
You holed yourself up
in your room every day
before you were a teacher.
Yeah, 'cause you
wouldn't give me
any spending money for figures,
you spiteful little beast.
Ow!
Ugh, shut up!
It's all my fault, per uge!
You know, I was going to
buy you a present today
to celebrate your one
month of hard work;
which was practically a miracle!
But if you wanna be
an ass, then forget it!
[JUNICHIRO]
Let's not be hasty!
Maybe we should go to that
anime store and talk this over!
Seriously, I'm sorry!
Please!
[SUZUNE]
Ugh! Fine!
[JUNICHIRO grunts]
Why are you acting weird?
Well, for the past few days,
I've had the distinct feeling
that someone was watching me.
[SUZUNE]
What?
Who? Where?
Are you sure?
Yeah, maybe I'm crazy.
Could be another symptom of YD.
Yeah.
Go figure.
That's your excuse for
everything these days.
So?
You see something you like?
Don't go too crazy.
[JUNICHIRO]
Heh. So glad you asked.
I present to you.
The best anime this season!
"Fwactal" volume one on Blu-ray!
[CROWD murmurs]
[SUZUNE]
It's good?
[JUNICHIRO howls]
You ignorant plebeian!
Yes! Of course it's good!
And it's gutsy, because it's
an original piece
not based off of a
manga or light novel!
The director, Tani-Kan,
is throwing down the gauntlet!
He said he'd retire
if it didn't sell!
The themes are so
incredibly complex
and the setting and
presentation are so unique
that the audience can
barely even keep up!
Okay. But why don't
you just order it online?
[JUNICHIRO] Again,
your ignorance wounds me!
If you buy it here
at Sonu-Map HQ,
you get a free,
limited-edition figurine!
Isn't it cute?
Well, I guess, if you
get a special figurine.
Okay!
[gasps]
Let's buy it.
[JUNICHIRO]
Huzzah!
[JUNICHIRO] Suzune may
not love anime like I do,
but I know she
likes collectibles.
Here. I hope you
enjoy it, ma'am.
[SUZUNE chuckles]
[JINICHIRO giggles]
Why, thank you!
[giggling]
[JINICHIRO]
Hm?
[JUNICHIRO]
That's an awfully heavy coat
to be wearing this time of year.
Hmm...
[YUKINO gasps]
Don't do something you're
gonna regret later.
[CHILDREN giggle]
Hand it over and I'll
put it back for you, okay?
[YUKINO gasps]
Help!
Pervert!
[CROWD] Huh?
[JUNICHIRO gasps]
[gasping continues]
[SUZUNE]
Huh?
No, I didn't do anything
to her, I swear!
All right, scumbag,
you're coming with me!
Let me explain! Hold on!
[ALL grunts]
Everything's okay,
miss, I've got him!
[YUKINO, CLERK grunt]
[JUNICHIRO]
Wait!
[SUZUNE] Move it!
[CLERK grunts]
[YUKINO, JUNICHIRO panting]
[JUNICHIRO]
Would you stop already?
Nobody's following us!
[YUKINO, JUNICHIRO panting]
[JUNICHIRO] When will
people learn my stats
are optimized for intelligence,
not athletics?
This is all your fault.
[JUNICHIRO]
Huh?
[grunts]
[JUNICHIRO gasps]
It's you.
You're the class rep,
Yukino, right?
I hate you so much.
I did this because you aren't
teaching our class properly!
Now, my practice exam
scores are dropping!
[JUNICHIRO]
I don't get it.
So you decided
to steal something?
That's a pretty weak excuse.
Apologize!
Never!
[JUNICHIRO]
Not to me.
[YUKINO gasps]
Tell Fwactal you're sorry!
Huh?
Audiences are still
blind to its genius
and home video sales
aren't quite profitable yet!
Don't you realize when an
idiot like you steals a copy,
the store has to sell 10
more just to break even?
Anime isn't some
mainstream interest!
Every single sale counts!
I think you lost me.
You know Tani-Kan's
career is on the line here.
If monsters like you
keep picking on him,
he's gonna be forced to retire!
[YUKINO]
I don't know who that is.
Maybe you were just doing
something stupid to vent,
but that can still make
other people suffer.
You can't just waltz
through your life
stepping over everyone else.
Got it?
[YUKINO gasps]
[YUKINO]
I envy you, Mr. Kagami.
Say wha--?
[YUKINO] Whether I buy into
the whole YD thing or not,
you get to do whatever you
want and no one stops you.
Your students still
have to worry about
their entrance exams, but that's
not your problem, I guess.
So, no!
It's you who's stepping over
everyone else, not me!
[JUNICHIRO]
Hold up!
[YUKINO gasps]
[JUNICHIRO]
This is my copy.
You take it.
Huh?
Please, there's no
need to thank me.
Spreading the faith is the
duty of every good otaku.
[YUKINO]
Hm...
[laughs]
[groans]
[SUZUNE]
I'm sorry, he's sorry,
--we're all very, very sorry!
--[JUNICHIRO whimpers]
[JUNICHIRO]
No!
I'm innocent!
Innocent, I tell you!
[SUZUNE]
Can it!
[GIRL chuckles]
[GIRL]
Too bad, Mr. Kagami.
You're all mine now.
[school bells ring]
No way I'm making lunch
for a pervert like you!
[JUNICHIRO groans]
I'm gonna starve to death.
[stomache growls]
Uhh... Huh?
[MINAKO]
Here! You hungry?
[JUNICHIRO]
Oh hey, Face Punch.
[gasps]
Did you make this yourself?
Are you kidding me?
Oh? Then who did?
Huh?
[chuckles]
Hello.
[JUNICHIRO] Hm. So Wicked
Blondie is a chef, is she?
Interesting. That's why
it smells like chalk.
It does not!
This is supposed
to be an apology!
Okay. I can live with that.
Whoa, it's beautiful!
[giggles]
I know, right?
So I'm having
trouble on this boss,
you think I can get
some tips from the pro?
Uh. You're still
playing that game?
I moved on ages ago.
It's crazy popular
right now!
[JUNICHIRO chuckles]
[MINAKO] It started when
you got our class into it,
but once the rest of the
students saw us playing,
they wanted in too.
Now, it's like a school
wide event, almost.
Pretty cool.
It's got one of those
dumb "free to play,
pay to win" systems if you
want the good items, though.
In other words,
poverty-stricken students like
me don't stand a chance.
But rules are rules, it's not
like they can be changed, right?
--[JUNICHIRO grunts]
--[MINAKO gasps]
[grunting]
[MINAKO]
Are you okay?
--[MIHO] Mr. Kagami!
--[JUNICHIRO] Oh, it's good!
[MINAKO, MIHO groan]
[MIHO]
Ugh, you big dork!
Don't freak out your poor
students like that!
So good!
[MIHO] Don't laugh
when I tell you this,
but I've actually wanted
to start a restaurant
ever since I was a kid.
My parents want
me to take over
the family motorcycle
business, though.
In the end, dreams are
just dreams, I guess.
[JUNICHIRO sighs]
But you, your dream is real.
[MIHO] Not only do you know
what you want for yourself,
you're doing whatever it
takes to make it happen.
[MINAKO] C'mon, it's not
that big of a deal.
I mean, we're still young.
Dreaming is practically our job.
Wow, what a line!
Just like an anime character!
You're there already!
[MINAKO huffs]
Don't be so coy.
You have a part in this too!
[JUNICHIRO]
Huh?
You're obligated to support me,
'cause if you hadn't hit me
with an inspiring anime line
of your own, I never would've
gone down this path!
"Support?" Like emotionally?
[panting]
[YOKO]
Miho, look!
It's Mr. Kagami.
[MINAKO, MIHO]
Hm?
[JUNICHIRO sighs]
What about me?
[GIRLS gasp]
[YOKO] Um. This is
all over the internet.
[JUNICHIRO]
Huh?
Oh...
Tell me that isn't
what it looks like.
[gasps]
[PRINCIPAL] I hope your side of
the story is very convincing.
Mr. Kagami.
[MALE STUDENT A]
Is this for real?
Yeah, that's him.
It doesn't look like it was
edited or anything, either.
He's in big trouble now.
What do you think, Miho?
What do I think?
Well, it's bad news, either way.
[MIHO]
Mm-hm.
He's weird, but not like that.
[YOKO]
Yeah, but look at the picture!
--What else could he be doing?
--[YUKINO] No, it was...
[MINAKO]
I'm telling you, he's innocent.
[FEMALE STUDENT C] What's your
take on this, Yukino?
I don't think we should
jump to conclusions
without knowing the full story.
More than anything,
I'm just disappointed in him.
You know. I kinda
liked his style.
Gotta say, I'll hate
to see him go.
Or I would have at least.
[gasps]
[MALE STUDENT B]
Hey, what happened?
He's fired!
[MALE STUDENT E]
He admitted it!
[FEMALE STUDENT C]
What?
[FEMALE STUDENT H]
You're kidding me!
[FEMALE STUDENT A]
That's crazy!
I can't believe
this is happening!
[gasps]
[YUKINO]
Hello.
[JUNICHIRO]
Hm?
Oh! The class rep!
Just finished cram school?
This is some weather, huh?
[YUKINO]
What are you talking about?
What happened?
Why didn't you tell
them the truth?
There was no point in
taking the fall for this.
You're innocent!
It's my fault.
You were just trying
to help me, and now--
[JUNICHIRO]
No, you got it all wrong.
[YUKINO grunts]
I've been wanting to quit
that stupid teaching job
since the day they hired me.
[JUNICHIRO]
What could I say?
You saw the picture.
Do you know anybody else
who dresses like this?
On the other hand.
No one would guess
that's you in the picture.
I do wonder who took
it in the first place,
but hey, either way,
that's behind us now.
[gasps]
[JUNICHIRO]
The important thing is.
I'm finally free.
You know what that means!
I can give my anime blog all
the attention it deserves!
I'll be back on top of the
rankings in no time flat!
[gasps]
Good luck and don't
forget to watch Fwactal!
[SUZUNE]
Are you kidding me?!
[crashing]
[yelps]
Calm down, dear sister,
there's no need for violence,
I assure you!
[growls]
This totally blows!
I get that you're not
really a molester,
and I get that you wanted
to protect that girl,
but you need to keep your job!
Why didn't you just explain
the situation to them?
It's simple enough!
Actually, I wasn't trying
to cover for her at all.
I finally got you
out of the house,
and you actually did a good job!
That's it. I'm going to the
principal's house right now
to tell him the truth!
Huh?
[SUZUNE grunts]
Wait, what's with the bat?
[PRINCIPAL yells]
[JUNICHIRO] I can see
the headlines now,
and after the news
spreads to the internet,
social justice warriors will
start spamming my site.
And then my precious
blog will be shut down!
No!
--[JUNICHIRO grunts]
--[SUZUNE gasps]
[JUNICHIRO]
Don't worry, Suzune.
It's fine. It was just
a temp position.
I'd get laid off eventually,
this way, at least I get to
protect one of my students.
I'm happy.
Really?
[JUNICHIRO]
Yeah.
[SUZUNE]
Okay, then.
Well, you get to pick out what
we eat for dinner tonight,
and I'll make it.
What sounds good to you?
[JUNICHIRO] A whole
table full of French fries!
[intercom chimes]
[FEMALE BROADCASTER]
All students,
please report to the auditorium.
We are holding a school-wide
emergency assembly.
I repeat...
[MALE STUDENT A] Welp,
we know what this is about.
[FEMALE STUDENT C sighs]
Guess that settles it, then.
[FEMALE STUDENT H]
Jeez, what a mess.
[MALE STUDENT B]
It's pretty clear cut,
looking at the picture.
[MINAKO]
You don't know that!
You weren't there!
[YUKINO whimpers]
[MALE STUDENT D]
Let's go.
[STUDENTS murmur]
[YUKINO gasps]
[MALE STUDENT D gasps]
Why aren't you letting us pass?
[FEMALE STUDENT E]
Tell us.
[FEMALE STUDENT B]
You're being weird, Yukino.
We have to go.
[FEMALE STUDENT A]
What's the deal?
[YUKINO pants]
Are you okay?
What's going on?
[YUKINO]
I...
It's my fault!
[STUDENTS chatter]
[PRINCIPAL clears throat]
[PRINCIPAL] Pardon me for
interrupting your classes.
But, with the deepest regret,
I have an announcement to make.
You see, due to some
various circumstances,
Mr. Kagami here is going to be
leaving our school, I'm afraid.
And that is
effective immediately.
[MALE STUDENT F]
Seriously?
[STUDENTS chatter]
Don't do it!
You can't quit on us!
We still need you!
This school year has
hardly even started!
You have to see it
through to the end!
[MIHO]
Yukino told us what happened!
You didn't do anything wrong!
We had a rough start,
but we really like you now!
You can't go, Mr. Kagami!
[FEMALE STUDENT C]
C'mon, just tell him the truth!
[MALE STUDENT F]
Don't quit on us!
[YUKINO]
Mr. Kagami.
If there's something you
still need to tell me,
you might want to do so quickly.
So that's the way
it's gonna be, huh?
[YUKINO]
I need to say something.
This isn't fair.
[JUNICHIRO]
Well.
Time to start the lesson.
[PRINCIPAL gasps]
I'm sorry, I--
Shut up!
[STUDENTS groan]
[gasps]
So here's the deal,
for whatever reason.
I'm being forced to
resign my position.
That's their decision,
and when they say
"due to various circumstances,"
you don't get to ask
what those are.
That's something you have
to deal with in our society.
The rules are the rules,
so don't question why!
[JUNICHIRO] Yeah right, like I'd
ever feed you that load of crap!
[STUDENTS]
Huh?!
[JUNICHIRO] But on this subject,
I do have one piece of advice.
You can't get by in
life by doing nothing
but following the rules.
They aren't made for people
like you and me, after all.
They're made for the
guys who make them.
These rules, designed to keep
you ignorant and powerless,
are going to hound you for
the rest of your lives.
So if you have a dream
that you want to fulfill,
then fight for it, and don't
be afraid to be yourself!
[phones buzzing]
[STUDENTS murmur]
[BOTH gasp]
[mumuring continues]
[YUKINO gasps]
Hm?
What's this?
[STUDENTS chatter]
The game.
[MIHO] He didn't make
this just now, did he?
[STUDENTS cheer]
[JUNICHIRO]
You see that?
I've given each of
you a special weapon,
limited by your imagination
and nothing else.
No money needed,
no grinding needed.
Customize it however you want,
be creative and win
by your own merits.
[gasps]
It's got one of
those "free to play,
pay to win" systems, so students
like me don't stand a chance.
But rules are rules, it's not
like they can be changed, right?
[BOTH giggle]
[JUNICHIRO] I don't care
if the game developer
set down the rules.
You decide how to play.
And that goes for life, as well.
[gasps]
Live by your own rules!
Sharpen the weapon
in your heart!
Don't quit, make reality
bow down to your will!
Just do that, and the
future will be all yours.
[ALL gasp]
[cheering]
My final lesson is over.
--[KOYOMI] No.
--[JUNICHIRO] Huh?
[KOYOMI] I'm afraid you have
much more teaching to do.
Yeah? Says who?
[KOYOMI] The chairperson
of Hiiragi Academy.
My name is Koyomi Hiiragi.
I'm here to recruit you.
Mr. Junichiro Kagami.
[KOYOMI] Don't think of what
happened as a tragedy,
Mr. Kagami, think of
it as an opportunity.
Hiiragi Academy can put your
talents to much better use,
I assure you.
Next episode.
Bravo team, Charlie Team.
I want you to lock
down all of Akihabara!
We have a new
teacher on the loose.
Period Three:
"Chase in Akihabara."
I didn't know you
hated teaching so much,
or perhaps there's something
you're not telling us?
[KOYOMI chuckles]