[JUNICHIRO]
Aw, yeah! First place! Bam!
[SUZUNE] Shut up!
[footsteps]
You have any idea
what time it is?!
[JUNICHIRO]
My "Super Bombastic Stories DX"
is first on the
anime blog charts!
[SUZUNE]
Get a job!
Loser!
Dear sister,
your brother cannot
"get a job," because he
suffers from YD.
[SUZUNE]
Hm? YD?
[JUNICHIRO groans]
Indeed. A crippling illness.
Those who suffer from it,
can only do what they
"yearn to do",
which in my case, is--
[gasps]
[SUZUNE yells]
[yelps]
Whoa, scary.
My precious!
[sighs]
You almost knocked my
beautiful waifu on the floor,
I'll have you know.
[SUZUNE]
You see this?
[JUNICHIRO]
Eh? Huh?
[SUZUNE] You're gonna be a
teacher, starting tomorrow.
[sighs]
A teacher, huh?
Given our current economy,
teaching is a safe source
of income, even part-time.
And with my intellect,
I'll likely be promoted quickly.
Since the job is
at my alma mater,
I'd be comfortable there,
and probably well-liked.
Sounds great!
But I must refuse!
Huh?
I got that YD
real bad, sis.
[growls]
[JUNICHIRO]
Heh.
[SUZUNE]
Then I'll beat it out of you!
[JUNICHIRO gasping]
No, don't do it!
--[SUZUNE grunting]
--[JUNICHIRO whimpers]
[STUDENTS chatter]
[PRINCIPAL] I must say,
this is truly a relief!
Mrs. Watanabe just
took her maternity leave
and we were scrambling
for a replacement!
[SUZUNE]
If you wear a coat,
you might fool people into
thinking you're respectable.
You know, like how
you used to be.
[JUNICHIRO] Well doesn't
hurt to pretend, right?
[PRINCIPAL]
Uh. Mr. Kagami. What's wrong?
Why did you hire me
without an interview?
I'm practically a
shut-in these days,
so I'm hardly a prime candidate.
I was kind of hoping
you'd pass, frankly.
[laughs]
Don't be so humble!
Everyone's heard of the
"Young Genius Junichiro!"
A physics visionary
at only 17 years old!
Your papers were
featured in "Nature,"
"Science" and many
other publications!
I tried to follow your work,
but I heard you turned down
offers from famous research
labs around the world!
What've you been doing?
Keeping my anime blog up
to date, for the most part.
Huh? Surely, that's a joke!
No, for real. I'm just sick
of science, that's all.
I mean, I think
anime's a lot cooler.
[GIRL] ♪Firing a bullet
straight into a romance!♪
♪Lovely Two-Hand, go!♪
I know this song!
It's the opening to Magical
Cannon Girl Bura-Kura!
Lovely Dreamy Two Hand!
Uh, what?
She's on the roof.
Mr. Kagami!
We still need to talk!
You filthy pleb!
This song is only 90 seconds
long, I'm about to miss it!
[PRINCIPAL
"You filthy pleb?"
[JUNICHIRO panting]
--[JUNICHIRO shouts]
--[GIRL] They call me a hero,
didn't you know?
♪Love-love bullets firing
and blood starts to flow!♪
♪Romance or combat, I just
say "come at me, bro"!♪
♪Baboom! Pchoo!♪
♪Haters to the back, please!♪
♪Evil down on its knees!♪
♪Love Soldier she's a killa,
Magical Cannon Girl Bura-Kura!♪
[clapping]
[gasps]
Who's there?
Whoa! Awesome!
It was like the real deal!
[grumbles]
I'm going to be
a voice actor.
[gasps]
Oh, really?
[MINAKO] I come here every
day to strengthen my
singing voice and build some
confidence for acting, too.
[MINAKO giggles]
Are you surprised?
I even enrolled in a
VA training school.
It's only a matter of
time before I'm a star!
[gasps]
How dare you.
You think voice acting
is that easy?!
[MINAKO]
Huh?
You went to a
training school?
You realize there's over
a thousand of those
all over the country!
That means tens of
thousands of rivals
are born every year and
only a hundred or so
can actually make a
living as voice actors!
That's a one in one
hundred thousand chance
of actually making it!
In other words,
you're more likely
to get in a car accident
on your way home today!
VAs are gods, understand?
Who cares if you can sing?
So what if your voice is cute?
That doesn't give you the right
to stand among their ranks!
The fans decide who--
--[MINAKO yells]
--[JUNICHIRO groans]
[thud]
I'm the one who
decides my fate.
[JUNICHIRO groans]
Haven't known her for 5 minutes
and she punches me in the face.
Not my kinda gal.
[STUDENTS chatter]
[FEMALE STUDENT A] I wonder
what the new physics teacher
is gonna be like.
[FEMALE STUDENT B] I heard
he was some super genius
who won a nobel prize for
some paper he published
in high school. Even crazier,
he used to go to this school.
[MIHO]
Minako!
Today I heard you singing
those stupid cartoon songs
on the roof again.
For real. What are
you like, five? C'mon!
Give that crap
up already, girl.
Wouldn't you rather hang
out with us instead?
[grunts]
Just like old times.
[JUNICHIRO]
Morning.
[gasps]
[MINAKO]
That weirdo from the roof?
[JUNICHIRO] Uh. Mrs. Watanabe
is on maternity leave...
This is the guy that's supposed
to be a super genius?
Looks like he doesn't
wanna be here.
[sighs]
[JUNICHIRO] Man, I'm really
not feeling this,
but this class isn't
gonna teach itself.
[laughs]
[groans]
[JUNICHIRO] Think. There has to
be a way to make this suck less.
[gasps]
[JUNICHIRO]
Wait a second.
[JUNICHIRO grunts]
Starting today,
I'm your new physics teacher.
Junichiro Kagami!
[STUDENTS chatter]
This here.
Is the address for
a smartphone game.
In order to get to know
each other better,
we will all be
playing this today!
[STUDENTS murmur]
[JUNICHIRO]
Furthermore.
Anyone who can beat me
will get an automatic 100
on their test next week!
[STUDENTS cheer]
Now, let's party!
If you want that easy A,
show me what you've got!
[STUDENTS cheer]
[JUNICHIRO] They may
think it's just a game,
but you can tell a
lot about someone
based on how they play
and react to other players.
It's the perfect way to
get inside their heads.
[MIHO]
Darn it!
[KEIKO]
What's up?
I just died.
[JUNICHIRO]
Miho Kitou,
she seems to be the
unofficial leader here.
Hm?
Is that Face Punch?
Kind of hoping she was
in someone else's class.
Huh?
Wow, I beat you!
--Let's have a rematch, okay?
--Me next!
[FEMALE STUDENT G]
I'm so bad at this!
[MALE STUDENT C] I think
I'm starting to get it now.
Loser.
[JUNICHIRO]
Huh...
[MINAKO grunts]
[FEMALE STUDENT I] Oh my gosh,
I think I'm totes gonna
--beat Mr. Kagami!
--[JUNICHIRO] Interesting.
I think I know where
everyone stands now.
The question is
what to do about it.
[MINAKO]
Uh.
[JUNICHIRO] Hm?
Hey, it's Face Punch!
You eat lunch here, too?
Face--? Ugh, you are not
gonna call me that.
And I am not eating with you!
[JUNICHIRO]
Just one thing.
The other kids.
Why are they picking on you?
[MINAKO gasps]
[gasps]
[JUNICHIRO] The main
culprits are Miho Kitou
and her two little friends.
But the other students
seem to be ignoring you,
even if they're not
outright bullying you.
You had the guts to sucker
punch me in the face.
Why are you putting
up with all of this?
You really are a weirdo, huh?
Ha! That's a laugh,
coming from you!
I heard the story.
You used to be some
fancy pants, but you gave up
and didn't do anything
remotely useful with yourself.
It's totally not true.
I designed an "Anywhere Door"
that could teleport you
wherever you wanted to go.
"Anywhere Door?"
Oh yeah, like that's real.
[JUNICHIRO]
It is.
[gasps]
Or to be more specific, it could
be real, if someone followed
the awesome theoretical
blueprints that I created.
I sent a paper about it to
one of those science magazines.
They really dug the idea.
And then, I finished
the blueprints.
People were flipping out, 'cause
I was still just a student.
[gasps]
Well, not like they
can make it, anyway.
We don't have the tech.
It won't exist until
the 22nd century.
It was fun, at least.
So, you gave up on research
after only one project?
I was never really
interested in academics
or physics research or
any of that boring stuff.
Got a case of YD.
What's that?
It means I can only do
what I "yearn" to "do".
Yeah?
Then what's wrong with
me being a voice actor?
'Cause voice actors are gods!
They breathe life into
the characters they play!
[giggles] All right,
I'll tell you why I don't
fight back against
Miho and her friends.
Because someday,
I'm going to be a hero.
What I'm facing now is my test.
Huh?
But I thought you were
gonna be a voice actor.
If I can become one of
your so-called "gods",
then being a hero should
be a piece of cake!
Interesting. So she
wants to be a hero.
Huh? Hmm.
[MINAKO sighs] I didn't realize
the lessons ran so late tonight.
[MINAKO gasps]
Is someone following me?
[MINAKO]
Better run.
[MINAKO grunts]
[MINAKO gasps]
[sighs]
--[PERVERT grunts]
--[MINAKO screams]
[PERVERT giggles]
So you only charge 5000
yen per touch, right?
[chuckles]
[groans]
[gasps]
[groaning]
You saved me!
[sighs]
Run away!
[MINAKO yells]
I'm a nerd! I only have
1 point in strength!
[yelling continues]
[MINAKO] I knew somebody
was following me.
What were you doing?
[JUNICHIRO grunts]
Well, for starters.
I stumbled upon this website.
[MINAKO gasps]
The "Higashi Shinmei
High Annex".
Have you seen this yet?
Ugly stuff.
[MINAKO gasps]
What?
[JUNICHIRO] Miho uploaded
your profile to the site.
It's a members only thing.
[gasps]
So, given the content,
I was a bit worried.
Wait, you were protecting me?
[JUNICHIRO]
It's a shame some moron
actually took that
profile seriously.
Well... Honestly, I can't
really blame him.
Up until just recently,
I was pretty bad.
I was having some serious
family issues back then.
I used to hang out
with Miho all the time.
We'd roam the streets
'til way late, start fights.
You know.
Just generally up to no good.
Then one day...
[MINAKO]
This world is nothing but crap.
There's no point in any of this.
I wish I could just
end it already.
I want to die.
I want to disappear.
Unlike Manga and Anime,
there's no hero to save you.
There's nothing left
for me to hope for.
--[computer beeps]
--[MINAKO gasps]
[MINAKO]
He's got a tip for me?
What does that mean?
--[computer beeps]
--[MINAKO gasps]
[MINAKO] "If there's no hero,
then become a hero."
[MINAKO] All of a sudden
my life had meaning.
Those words gave me strength.
So, it turns out that was a
quote from Sergeant Saunders
in an anime called "Magical
Cannon Girl Bura-Kura."
[grunts]
[MINAKO] Finding that out
really opened my eyes.
Even if something
is a work of fiction,
it can still help people.
I will use it to help.
Even if it is by myself.
If I can act, if I can keep
true to those inspiring words.
Then that's enough.
I could become a hero!
A hero, huh?
[STUDENTS chatter]
Uh.
Hey, lately, have you been
getting some more attention?
[MINAKO grunts]
[MIHO] We've been trying
to help out with your PR.
Like, raise some
buzz or whatever.
[KEIKO, YOKO chuckles]
Speaking of help,
in your line of work,
you gotta take extra
good care of your voice!
I found a neat recipe online.
This drink we made is supposed
to do wonders for your throat.
[FEMALE STUDENT B] I heard
Miho made her drink some juice
with chalk in it!
[JUNICHIRO]
Hm?
That's going too far!
She went to the nurse!
What happened?
[MINAKO gasps]
Nothing. I drank expired juice.
The nurse said I'd be just fine.
Your voice is hoarse!
It's no big deal!
Just think of it as
a cool new sound!
I mean, maybe I can voice
boy characters now, too!
Miho's work again, I presume.
[MINAKO]
Stay out of this, Mr. Kagami.
This is my past, and so
it is my struggle.
If I can't overcome
this on my own,
the whole thing's meaningless.
Sometimes, walking the hero's
path can be a little lonely.
[JUNICHIRO]
Is that so?
[MINAKO sighs]
♪Firing...♪
[sobs]
[JUNICHIRO] Face Punch,
it seems you haven't learned
how to stay in character yet.
[school bells ring]
--[MIHO] Did someone prank us?
--[YOKO] Well, this is lame.
[chattering]
[JUNICHIRO]
Wicked Blondie. Right on time.
[MIHO]
Why the hell am I "wicked"?
Wanna tell me why you called
us all up to the roof, weirdo?
Okay.
Just wondering why you like
picking on Minako Kanou so much.
--[YOKO, KEIKO gasp]
--[MIHO] We don't!
We have no idea what
you're talking about, sir!
Isn't that right girls?
Oh really? Just what
I wanted to hear!
This'll be fun!
Not as naughty as
late-night anime,
but I'll try to make do.
[gasps]
Have a nice day, ladies.
[GIRLS]
Hm?
Okay. Time to start the lesson.
[YOKO]
Kagami's onto us.
Should we do something?
Maybe take it easy for a while?
[KEIKO] You think he hacked
the Annex site or something?
Uh, don't be dumb!
Whoever put that site together
made it nice and secure.
No way Mr. Kagami is that l33t.
He's just a nerd.
Not every otaku is
a hacker or whatever.
[phone beeps]
[YOKO]
Mm?
[gasps] Miho, did you
just message me?
Huh? Uh-uh.
[YOKO]
But look!
It's an Annex message
from you, no doubt.
[MIHO]
What does it say?
[YOKO gasps]
[MIHO]
"Look up?"
[GIRLS]
Huh?
[ALL scream]
[coughing]
What is this?
[YOKO]
Chalk... powder.
[JUNICHIRO laughs]
[GIRLS]
Huh?
[laughing continues]
[coughing]
[JUNICHIRO] You stand accused
of the crime of bullying!
[GIRLS]
Huh? Uh...
[JUNICHIRO]
In the name of Justice,
Justice Man will punish you!
Justice Man?
You didn't even change clothes!
And that stupid voice
is barely different!
[ALL gasp]
Huh? You're using a
tablet to record us?
[JUNICHIRO] Not only that,
I'm livestreaming it
all over the world as we speak!
The title is "Justice Man vs
Bully High School Girls:
Extreme Butt Whipping,"
which is much less
dirty than it sounds.
What?
[JUNICHIRO]
Well, look at that.
Three discussion
threads already!
You're nuts! We will so
have you fired for this!
You can't prove we
did anything wrong!
[JUNICHIRO]
Can't I?
Ha! Because I've been
perusing your chat logs
from the high school Annex site,
and they tell another story.
[ALL gasp]
No way. He did hack it.
[JUNICHIRO]
That's what you think I did?
How quaint.
No, hacking wasn't necessary,
my stupefied students.
I created it.
[ALL gasp]
There were quite a
few otaku in my class
when I was your age and we
wanted to cook up a way
to share pictures and other
such things we found online.
Now I find you ruined
my masterpiece.
Your retribution is at hand.
Are you ready?
--[KEIKO, YOKO whimper]
--[MIHO] We're screwed!
If he can read all our messages,
there's no way we
can get outta this!
Let's see, as a
suitable punishment,
I think I'll take all your
personal information,
and dump it in this thread
that's so popular right now.
No! Don't even joke about that!
You can't give out our home
addresses, that's crazy!
We were just upset 'cause Minako
stopped hanging out with us!
It was all in good fun, gah!
That's right!
It wasn't bullying!
No, I suppose that
it wasn't, was it?
[KEIKO, YOKO sigh]
'Kay, then!
To be specific,
what you did was a crime.
Criminal law,
article 204, Injury.
article 222, Intimidation.
And finally, criminal
law article 61,
Inducement of Assault.
[gasps]
Come on, that's enough.
[JUNICHIRO]
Just helping you with PR!
Hope you enjoy all the
attention you're gonna get!
Starting...
...now!
No way!
--[phone buzzes]
--[ALL gasp]
Oh! A phone call already!
You better answer it!
If you don't they might call
your parents or the school next!
Uh, hello?
[JUNICHIRO snickers]
Trolled!
Huh?
[JUNICHIRO]
Did I scare you?
Before you ask, I did make
an entire fake video stream,
complete with comments.
I take this seriously.
[ALL gasping]
Now you know what it feels like
to be on the receiving end.
[ALL whimper]
[MINAKO]
Hold on, Mr. Kagami!
Oh, hey, what's up, Face Punch.
What the heck did
you do to them?
Nothing special. Let's just say
I gave an extracurricular lesson
to a trio of troubled students.
[GIRLS whimper]
I said I wanted to get through
this on my own, didn't I?
What even made you think
I needed you to interfere?
If there's no hero,
then become a hero, right?
[gasps]
[JUNICHIRO] But Sergeant
Saunders from Bura-Kura
still gets plenty of help
from Corporal Hartman
when she finds
herself in a pinch.
[gasps]
[JUNICHIRO] Even Batman
has Robin for a sidekick.
[sighs]
[JUNICHIRO] Being a hero
may be a lonely fight,
but that doesn't mean
you have to do it alone.
[laughs]
[JUNICHIRO]
Right, Little Rabbit?
[gasps]
Yeah, I know. "YD."
But there is still plenty
of stuff I yearn to do.
[MINAKO gasps]
[JUNICHIRO] And that concludes
my lesson for the day.
He knew, all this time.
[MINAKO] He saved me.
He changed my life.
K.Y! Thank you!
[GIRL laughs]
[GIRL] What an
interesting teacher.
Very intriguing indeed.
[MINAKO] Hi, it's Minako Kanou,
AKA Face Punch!
I guess I can
tolerate that nickname
for the preview
at least, seeing as
Mr. Kagami saved my life twice.
Anyway, next episode,
our YD hero runs afoul of
the class representative!
Let's see if his
homegrown otaku wisdom
can get him out of this one!
Wait, what's this about
him molesting a girl?
Period two, "The Laws of
Society." If that rumor's true,
you're gonna get more
than just a face punch!
By the way, what was up
with that girl at the end?