Hey! Don't change that channel!
You don't wanna miss
a second of this one!
Huh? The twins
aren't getting along?
This is getting complicated!
I'll have to give that idol
a lesson face-to-face!
All teachers are looking for
diamonds in the rough,
and I, Junichiro Kagami,
the Ultimate Otaku Teacher,
always find them first!
Family... Kick!
It's time I came clean.
I'm actually the leader
of Black Oracle Neo,
and I can't stand
letting something fun
slip through my fingers.
Ready? Okay,
it's time to start the show!
No, you've got it all wrong!
If things stay the way
they are now, well then, I...
I'll quit! I'll leave my job
as a singer for good!
You, ah...
What do you mean?
[sighs]
Is something wrong?
[screams]
Is that Komi-Ryu
from the 5th Queens?
N-No way.
But on the TV they said
you're doing a TV interview.
Like, right now.
[MALE MANAGER 20A] This is bad!
She won't answer her phone!
[CEO] Where did she run off to
and why is she ruining my day?
We've got to get my sister's
life back on track.
I would do anything,
but she won't listen to me.
So please!
Don't worry.
Give me the details.
You mean it?
Actually, before that...
Hey, Anime Girl,
you're in the broadcasting
club, aren't you?
Wait, what's going on?
Mm. Let's just say
you flipped on his switch.
Huh? What switch?
He's usually super lazy.
Til something sparks his fancy.
Let's go, Idol Sister.
Everything is set!
Uh?
Uhh?
[JUNICHIRO] Shinmei Elementary.
Your alma mater, right?
[STUDENTS chatter]
[MALE STUDENT 20A]
Hurry!
[MALE STUDENT 20B]
Lighting ready?
[MALE STUDENT 20C]
Yeah!
[MALE STUDENT 20D] We're all
good to go over here!
[MALE STUDENT 20E] Give us
one last second, then!
[NAGARE]
This is... Wow.
Jeez. Hey! Did you have to
spring this on us last-minute?
I brought every webcam
and laptop I could find,
so I hope this is enough!
Perfect! Nice job
on the lighting, too.
All right guys, this'll be good!
Thanks for the hard work!
[STUDENTS]
Sure!
I, uh...
I got in contact
with some old buddies
that used to go here
and they were able to
hook us up with the venue.
Then, since half of them
are in my class anyway,
I got the Icho Academy
broadcasting club
to provide the equipment.
They act like it was a pain,
but they didn't have
anything better to do.
So what now?
Well, we're going to
broadcast online, of course.
You're missing your
big interview, right?
You'll just have to make your
announcement from here!
Huh? I'm not ready!
[JUNICHIRO] If you can't be
responsible about your own job,
you can't criticize your sister
for the choices she makes.
I know you didn't
make this decision lightly
and you're just thinking
about your family.
But still, you have
a responsibility
to your fans, too,
and you can't leave them
in the dark like this.
You're a pro.
You can make this mishap
look like a special event.
[MALE MANAGER 20A]
Someone claiming to represent
Komi-Ryu just called!
He said something about her
doing an internet broadcast?
A what? Right now?
Hmm...
Either way around,
we don't have much choice
in the matter. I'll give
the producer the news.
Hi everyone at home.
It's me, Komi-Ryu!
I'm sorry I couldn't
make it to the studio today.
'Cause right now I'm visiting
my old elementary school!
The point is, this new
project I'm working on
is very special to me.
So I wanted to announce this
from a special place.
I hope it's not too much
of a pain for everyone.
Anyway, I have
a song for you guys.
It's the theme song for the
drama Twin Moon Princesses,
"Together."
[MALE DIRECTOR 20A] I don't know
who's doing the camera work,
but it looks solid to me.
[MALE PRODUCER 20A]
And I bet the surprise factor
has attracted a good amount
of extra viewers.
Let's just hope she doesn't
pull something like this again.
[JUNICHIRO] That's a wrap!
Nice work, everyone!
[inhales deeply, exhales]
[JUNICHIRO]
Anyway, thanks again!
I'll let you know
if I make friends with
any other pop singers.
Okay!
[NAGARE] Uh, excuse me.
Are you Mr. Kagami's students?
Huh? Oh yeah, we are.
It's awkward,
but there's something
I need you to clear up.
[KANAN, KOUTARO]
Uhh...
I mean, why did Mr. Kagami
do this? It's my fault.
I'm the one who didn't
go to the studio.
But when he found out,
he acted like the whole thing
was his responsibility.
Figures. He probably thought
"pop star skips TV gig
to make an online broadcast
from her alma mater"
was a fun scenario.
You gotta be kidding.
It's funny,
when you put it like that,
it almost sounds like a joke,
but I thought the same thing.
Who cares! Let him
be a weirdo as long as
he's a weirdo that
helps people get stuff done!
Mm-hmm! And it's fun
to watch at least!
[NAGARE]
Thanks for everything.
And I think
what you said was right.
If I can't even fight for
my own place in this world,
I have no right to tell my
sister that hers is wrong.
It feels like you can
see right through me.
I should be ashamed of myself.
If I want your help so bad,
I should just be honest.
For starters,
I'll tell you why I really
want my sister to
quit Black Oracle Neo.
I shouldn't even
be here today.
It was supposed to be Taki
standing up on
that stage, dancing.
She's the reason
I have this career!
What do you mean?
I've never told anyone
this story before.
It's not something I'm
proud of, so you'll see why.
I still remember clearly.
Something terrible happened
the morning of my big audition.
All of a sudden, my stomach
started hurting so bad,
they had to take me
to the hospital.
[TAKI]
Hold on, Nagare!
[ambulance sirens wail]
Is she okay?
Yes, but it's
acute appendicitis.
She, uh, has an
audition to go to.
Will she make it?
[MALE DOCTOR 20A]
Oh no, definitely not.
We're going to have to operate.
Now what?
So, I take it you missed
the audition, then.
I wasn't even conscious
for the audition.
But they called the next day.
I passed? But how?
[CEO] Don't worry about that.
Your lessons start in a week.
I have high hopes
for you! See ya soon!
[TAKI] You got it?
Congrats! That's awesome!
I guess,
but I don't get it.
I didn't even
make it to the aud--
"Hey guys! Nagare here!"
Taki.
Heh. They only saw
like, one photo of you,
so all I had to do
was copy your hairstyle
and I was good to go!
Lucky you've got
such a talented sister here
to watch your back, huh?
Just kidding.
I'm not even
half as good as you,
so if I can make it,
you'll be fine!
So then...
I let them know
about the situation.
I went to visit
their office as soon as
I got out of the hospital.
I told them I couldn't
take the job.
[CEO] It's fine.
I'm not firing you.
I can't accept the job
when I didn't even make it--
Let me tell you something
about that audition.
That entire day,
there was only one girl
who gave a performance
that impressed me
and that was Nagare Komiya.
Or, that's who she said
she was, at least.
Though it was clear
that something was up.
He already knew?
Yeah. The CEO saw through
Taki's plan right away.
But he wasn't angry at all.
It's more like he was curious.
So who are you really?
Nagare Komiya.
No point in lying.
You're plenty talented
and your face looks just
like the girl in the photo,
but you're lacking
something, I'm afraid.
What do you mean?
You're too flat.
Huh?
[grunts]
[sighs]
Shoulda known this
wouldn't be so easy.
I insist that you
give Nagare this job.
First you try to
cheat the system,
then you make demands?
Do you want me to call security?
So, why don't you
tell me what you thought
about my performance?
It was everything
we're looking for.
Well, all right then, good.
'Cause Nagare Komiya's
even better than me.
And trust me,
I'm her twin sister.
I've seen her perform
for years now.
She's gonna knock your
socks off. You have my word.
Interesting. I like it.
[CEO]
Nagare gets the job.
What? But sir!
We're looking for
diamonds in the rough
and she's our
best bet right now.
We have to be willing
to take a risk
and if the girl doesn't cut it,
then we'll just fire her.
Mr. Gomi!
[CEO] And what does our little
party crasher here intend to do?
I'll take responsibility
if that's what you're asking.
You'll never see me anywhere
in show business again, okay?
From here on out, I swear it's
my sister and my sister alone.
[NAGARE] Even knowing the truth,
he still wanted me onboard,
so I had to agree.
He just told me to
live up to Taki's praise,
which of course,
I was adamant about, too.
This never would've
happened without her,
so I had to work
as hard I could,
so I wouldn't let her down
no matter what.
[NAGARE] I moved to the city,
took as many lessons
as they offered
and practiced in every
spare minute I could find.
Then before I knew it,
I made my debut
as the lead member
of the 5th Queens.
[CROWD cheers]
[NAGARE] Then,
after my first concert...
You were great!
Can you spare time for a fan?
Taki!
I told you! Always knew
you were born to be a star!
All those years of me cheering
you on really paid off!
Anyway, I'd better go now.
Wouldn't want anyone else
catching me here.
We need to talk! Wait!
Don't feel bad.
If you found the place
where you belong,
then I can do the same thing!
We're sisters, after all.
[NAGARE] After that,
she formed Black Oracle Neo.
She says she's happy,
but I know that's not
where she belongs!
If you saw her audition tape,
you'd understand.
She's as good as I am.
No, honestly,
she's much better than me,
but because of that stupid
promise she made,
she'll never get a chance
to show the world!
I know I didn't ask her
to do it, but I feel like
I stole her whole life
away from her!
[crying]
Now it all makes sense.
[cell phone chimes]
Mr. Kagami?
[cell phone beeps]
[JUNICHIRO] We're going
to get rid of all those
little misconceptions of yours.
Come visit me
after work. Mr. Kagami.
[NAGARE]
Where are we going?
[JUNICHIRO] I know it looks
kinda shady from the outside,
but they're holding
an event here.
What kind of event?
Well. Details later.
For now, let's get
you changed. Here.
Okay, I put it on,
but this outfit
is really not okay!
Also, why does my hair
need to be like Taki's?
Idol Sister, as of right now
you're Taki Komiya.
Huh?
[JUNICHIRO]
And like she did for you,
you're going to act
as her emergency stand-in
for what will be a very
important performance.
[NAGARE] Can we
talk about this first?
[JUNICHIRO]
No time!
This is another
important place for Taki.
And you'll see why!
[JUNICHIRO] It's the Fraternal
Force Family Rangers
Fan Gathering!
Since you missed
your own audition,
this'll be a chance to
prove your sisterly power!
My what? I still don't
see the point in this!
You will, though.
[CHIYO]
Hey, Taki!
[laughs]
Oh, you made it!
I'm so happy!
Who are you?
You are such a
little kidder, aren't you?
Why, I'm your soulmate,
Chiyo, of course!
I don't know what happened
with that group meeting
you were supposed to
go to tonight,
but as long as you're here,
we can win this
sing-off for sure!
This venue doesn't
look like much,
but it's popular
for fan gatherings.
In fact, it's so popular that
the different fan groups
have these little
performance showdowns
to decide who
can use the space.
And tonight a new group
is challenging
your sister's group
for their time slot.
Oh, wow.
By the way,
your sister has defended
the Family Rangers slot
for two years now.
All by herself.
[gasps]
As soon as
the performance is done,
everyone here uses
an electronic voting system
to determine the score.
If they tie, then that means the
defending team is the winner.
It sounds fancy, but it's
just like sending a text.
Well, you're up
after the next girl.
[CHIYO]
It's gonna be tough.
We're facing the
Beast Band Rocker Rangers;
which are as cool
as they sound.
Also, I know our show
has more heart and all,
but they kind of have the edge,
seeing as their show
is still on the air and
ours is like, ten years old.
[CROWD cheers]
[RANDOM MAN 20A]
Go Go Rock Rangers!
[RANDOM MAN 20B]
Dude! A perfect score!
Eat it, Family Rangers!
Awesome! Thanks, guys!
[CHIYO] That girl, Moemi,
is training at an actual school
for performers right now.
Talk about playing dirty.
[laughs]
[MOEMI]
Hmm.
You're the one
I've heard so much about!
The famous Taki Komiya.
Ugly!
You only held
this slot for so long
'cause you never
had to face me!
Look, you're finished.
You might as well
just go home now!
Take a lesson
from a real pro, rookie.
[MOEMI] I hope you
enjoyed the show!
You okay?
Uh-huh. Ugh.
Don't worry about me.
I'm ready to go.
So all it took
to get you all fired up
was a little trash talk
from a fellow performer?
[NAGARE]
She didn't insult me.
I'm angry because
she's disrespecting my sister.
Gonna be okay
with no rehearsal time?
[NAGARE] It's no different
than what Taki did for me.
Besides, I'm the one
who introduced her
to Family Rangers.
[NAGARE gasps]
[NAGARE] Just performing
the song won't be enough.
Tonight, I'm Taki.
She would get a perfect score.
She would win over
the opposition, too.
Am I really
as good as her?
[NAGARE whimpers]
[JUNICHIRO]
Hey, Idol Sister, look.
Taki gave me this.
Now think. Isn't this guy
the reason why you're here?
For the show?
[JUNICHIRO] For the
meaning behind the show.
Black Oracle Neo might not
be a real super-powered
fraternal fighting force,
but it is about family.
And that's why your sister
wants to make it
like the old Black Oracle.
[NAGARE]
Mmm.
[JUNICHIRO] A group that comes
together to accomplish
something great, with a bond
that can never be broken.
Of course, she only
started taking an interest
in this community
after you left town.
I'm sure you understand
the significance of that.
Yes, of course I do,
but I'm scared.
That makes it
even worse if I lose.
Taki's fought so hard
to keep this position,
but I didn't even know
this was a thing until today!
I'm just some crummy stand-in!
How am I supposed to
compete with her?
I can't! I'm not as talented
as her, or as strong.
You know, if I
mess this up for her
when it means so much,
I'll never be able
to forgive myself!
[JUNICHIRO] I'm sure that's how
she felt during your audition.
[NAGARE gasps]
[JUNICHIRO] Your entire future
was hanging in the balance,
and in her mind at least,
she was nothing more
than an inferior replacement.
The stage may be different,
but once again your hearts
are in the same place.
There's no "game over."
Not now.
You need to press "Start" to
"Continue" to clear this stage
and move on in the game of life.
[RANDOM MAN 20C] The last group
already got a perfect score.
Might as well go home.
[CHIYO] There's one more!
Just watch one more!
[MOEMI] Looks like I've already
won over the audience.
Sucks to be you.
[NAGARE] ♪ Our family
ties will never die. ♪
Whoa, wait.
--♪ All you brothers from.... ♪
--Wow!
She's doing that without a mic?
[RANDOM MAN 20D] Is she
an opera singer or something?
Family Ragners!
[CROWD yells, gasps]
You take a lesson
from a real pro, rookie.
[NAGARE] The Family Rangers
opening theme.
"Family Ties"! Here goes!
[NAGARE] It's been years,
but it's like the lyrics
are engraved in my heart.
Like my muscles remember
every dance move.
Nagare, you're the best!
Do it again for me!
[NAGARE] I remember now.
This was the first song
I sang for Taki.
The first one I did a dance for.
The beginning of everything.
Yay! I love it!
That is so awesome!
Really?
Yeah! You should
totally do this on TV!
You'll be a big star!
[NAGARE]
I owe everything to you.
I just hope I can pay it back.
Thank you, Taki.
[CROWD murmurs]
[cell phones beeping]
[RANDOM MAN 20E]
Another perfect score!
The Family Ranger fans
defend their spot!
[gasps]
Nice job. You finally
passed the audition.
It took a while, huh?
Guess so.
I feel free. Finally. I think
I can face Taki now.
Thank you.
[chuckles]
It's the Family Rangers
who saved the day this time.
Not me.
Oh, yeah, they have
a changing room over there,
if you need one.
[NAGARE]
Right.
[CHIYO] I'm so glad
Taki made it after all!
Yeah, the competition
was tough this time.
We thought we were done for!
[JUNICHIRO]
I bet! He-heh!
[NAGARE]
Mm!
[JUNICHIRO] She's taking
an awful long time to change.
Wonder what's up?
[NAGARE] This is Nagare Komiya,
AKA Komi-Ryu!
I sure am happy I was finally
able to pay my sister back
for the whole audition thing.
Next episode,
I get kidnapped!
But never fear,
because the Family Rangers
come to save the day!
Wait, what?
They're not even real!
Period twenty-one,
"Here Come the Family Rangers!"
You lay a finger on my sister
and I'll strike you down!
Family Final Dragon Crush!
Is this an action anime now
and I missed the memo?