[JUNICHIRO]
I have YD.
You say you've never
heard of it? What?
I like wearing yukata on dates?
Or yummy dinners?
Wrong!
It's a debilitating illness
where you can only do
what you yearn to do.
[YUKINO]
Help! Pervert!
[YOKO] Um. This is
all over the internet.
[JUNICHIRO]
Oh...
[MINAKO]
Don't do it.
You can't quit on us!
I'm sorry, I--
[PRINCIPAL gasps]
You can't get by in life
by doing nothing but
following the rules.
Sharpen the weapon
in your heart!
Make reality bow
down to your will!
Just do that, and the
future will be all yours.
I'm the chairperson of
Hiiragi Academy, Koyomi Hiiragi.
And I am here
today to recruit you.
Mr. Junichiro Kagami.
What, like, for the horde?
Pardon?
No, I've heard
about your splendid
achievements at
East Shinmei High.
Yet, for some unfortunate
reason or another,
it would appear that you won't
be teaching at this "renowned"
school any longer and will be
needing new employment.
Well, one man's trash is another
man's treasure, as they say,
and who am I to pass on a
golden opportunity like this?
Wait, did you call me "trash"?
I know what's on
your mind right now.
I can see it on your face,
as plain as day.
[gasps]
"A sexy girl like her
surely has options,
so why would she be the
chairperson of a school?"
[JUNICHIRO]
That's not what I'm thinking!
And while I am
loaded with options,
I'm more than just a pretty
face. I'm also the granddaughter
of the previous Hiiragi
Academy chairperson.
[JUNICHIRO]
What's with the options?
If you've got so much going on,
then why come and find me?
It's not like it's hard
to find elite teachers
who are looking for
work these days.
[sighs]
My only claim to fame
is that article I
wrote five years ago.
It's not like I'm
a hot commodity.
[KOYOMI] It would appear you
misunderstand my intentions.
Publishing a paltry science
paper or two is insignificant.
I'm aiming for something
much higher than that.
Mr. Kagami. My goal
is to change Japan.
We as a people must
continue to prosper.
So, My school promotes
forward-thinking
through education.
Our students develop values
based on neither economics,
nor standard industry capital.
[KOYOMI] My vision
is simple, yet profound.
Amusing Country, Japan!
In order to achieve this,
I must enlist amusing people,
such as yourself.
So I implore you, please
consider my generous offer.
This country needs you
and your eccentricities.
Take some time
and think it over.
I will visit your home tomorrow
morning to hear your response.
Farewell.
That's not what
I was expecting.
[SUZUNE]
Huh? You found another job?
That's impressive!
But kinda weird that we'll
be going to the same place.
Wait. I thought your school
was called Icho, sis.
Surprised you remembered,
but yeah,
it's like a division
of Hiiragi Academy.
That means Hiiragi's
the nice school,
and Icho's for
underprivileged kids?
[whines]
That's a face. You look
like mom and dad
found your Boys' Love
manga under your bed.
Right! 'Cause I'd have
something like that!
[JUNICHIRO]
Uh...
Icho Academy is open
to the general public.
Hiiragi, on the other hand,
is only for kids
with special talents.
Everybody who attends there is
super mysterious and dangerous.
We Icho students won't even
go near the Hiiragi building.
They've got us
totally freaked out.
Rumor has it some students
were never heard from again
after they got lost and wound
up on Hiiragi's campus.
It sounds more like a haunted
mansion than a school.
[SUZUNE]
They get great teachers, too,
but the students
are so hardcore,
they don't stand a chance.
One time, they got a Nobel
Prize winner to come teach,
and he didn't even
last three days.
Is that so?
I guess little Miss Options
wasn't lying to me after all.
"Miss Options?"
[JUNICHIRO]
Hmm...
Whatever.
The important thing is,
you won't be an unemployed
waste of space again.
--[WOMAN screams]
--You're back in the game.
What a relief.
[KOYOMI]
I've made my decision.
We've been over this.
No, it's my call
as chairperson,
and I expect you
to understand that.
Good, thank you.
[KOYOMI laughs]
[sighs]
What should I do? Hmm.
[gasps]
[JUNICHIRO]
Crap!
I almost forgot
what day it was!
I gotta get moving!
[gasps]
I've got some bad news.
[SUZUNE] I looked all
over the house for him!
I don't know where
he could have gone,
he knows it's an important day.
Ugh!
When I find him, he's gonna be
sorry he missed your meeting!
Can't you make things easy for
once in your miserable life?
It's a great offer, too, why do
you have to be such a flake?
Ugh!
[KOYOMI] There's no need
for you to get worked up.
Huh?
The only way we can
know for certain
what he's thinking is
to ask him in person.
So all we need to
do is go find him.
Yeah, I guess, but how?
[helicopter buzzes]
[gasps]
Alright. There's our ride!
[SUZUNE]
Uh... Huh?
Man, I figured she was rich,
but I didn't think she was,
like, crazy, stupid rich.
Hey, uh. What's the plan?
Where are we going exactly?
I'm confused here,
what are we doing?
We're following my
leads on your brother
so that we may have our meeting.
[SUZUNE]
Hm?
Our first report should be
coming in any moment now.
[PILOT] Miss Koyomi.
Tango Two is on the line.
Patching in.
[YOKOYAMA]
This is Tango Two, Yokoyama.
Our satellites have
located the target.
Holy cow.
[YOKOYAMA] The target is
currently on the move.
It appears he is
heading for Akihabara.
Good work. Now.
Commence Operation:
Crimson Flower.
Set up mobile headquarters
on Chuo Street, Akihabara.
Be advised: do not
disrupt civilians.
Junichiro Kagami is
your only concern.
I don't want any
collateral damage
in our pursuit of the target.
--Have I made myself clear?
--"Collateral damage?"
That sounds a bit
excessive to me.
[KOYOMI]
It's not. But never mind.
We will find your brother.
And we will discuss
his future employment.
[sighs]
How amusing.
I'm sure you'll have
plenty of lovely tricks
to show me in our
afternoon chase, Mr. Kagami.
[giggles]
[helicopter buzzes]
[CROWD]
Huh?
Come on. This way.
Wait, hold on a second.
I'm gonna try calling
him one more time, okay?
[JUNICHIRO] Hey! What's up?
You need something?
Yeah, I do. Where are you?
[JUNICHIRO]
Can you go somewhere quieter
so you don't have to yell at me?
I wanna yell at you!
You blew off your meeting!
Did you forget the chairperson
was coming to see you?
Oh, I didn't think it
was that big of a deal.
I mean, sure, Options wanted
to recruit me,
but I never said I'd accept
her job offer, did I?
[gasps]
C'mon, you know
I've got that YD.
I'm too antisocial to yearn
for a nine-to-five job.
And they won't learn
if I don't yearn.
So, yeah. Sorry, sis,
I'm not doing it.
[gasps]
Anyway, I gotta go.
I'm busy with stuff that has
nothing to do with teaching.
See ya later!
[growls]
You little bum!
It would appear your
negotiations have failed.
I'm so sorry, ma'am!
I'll make him apologize
to you, I swear!
One more thing before you go.
Yes?
[KOYOMI]
Here.
[gasps]
If you happen to locate
him before we do, call me.
This is a direct line
to my personal cell.
[SUZUNE]
I will. Thank you! Alright!
He's lucky to have
such a caring sister.
Now, our little game of
hide and seek has begun.
Ready or not,
Mr. Kagami, here I come.
[SUWA]
This is Yankee One, Suwa.
In position.
Tango Two, Yokoyama.
Alpha One, Iwata here.
In position.
The squads are in place
and awaiting orders!
Operation White
Flower Bud is a go!
All units.
Begin special operations.
Target specifications:
Name, Junichiro Kagami.
Height, five foot seven.
Has red hair and eye glasses.
He also wears a lab coat
over a pink hoodie.
Currently somewhere
in Akihabara.
Report immediately
upon sighting.
I repeat, target
specifications...
[FEMALE OPERATOR]
Attention engineering;
tap into mobile
phone GPS location.
Double-check
security camera feeds.
--Report as necessary.
-- [KOYOMI laughs]
[KOYOMI] Akihabara isn't
called the "Electronic Town"
for nothing.
Its security is assured by its
numerous surveillance cameras.
Which I happen
to have access to
thanks to our connections
with the police.
And if that doesn't
serve our purposes,
I can tap into the
satellite feeds as well.
With so many watchful eyes,
there isn't anyone who gets
by without being seen.
We could catch an ant trying
to get in if we wanted to.
And to top it all off,
I've employed two-hundred
agents to search on foot.
Our game is in motion.
Let's see what wins:
my near limitless resources,
or your talents.
I look forward to seeing
what you are capable of
Mr. Kagami.
This is Oscar One, Azuma.
I have eyes on the target.
Currently moving
from area D3 to D6.
I am in pursuit.
[AZUMA]
Awaiting instructions.
[MIZOGAMI]
Tango Three, Mizogami.
I see him.
He's approaching Anumate.
HQ? Miss?
What're my orders?
Let him wander
a bit more.
Follow him inside.
[MAEKAWA] This is
Whiskey One, Maekawa!
Target is leaving the building!
[AGENTS grunt]
[JUNICHIRO]
Hmm...
[AZUMA]
Oscar One, Azuma reporting!
I'm sorry.
We lost sight of him in area D6.
That's bad news;
our target seems to know the
area like the back of his hand.
I expected nothing less.
If there were no
challenge to the chase,
then it wouldn't be
terribly amusing, would it?
[MALE ENGINEER] His mobile
GPS signal just went dark.
He must have turned
off his phone.
Attention!
All units converge on his
last known location, D6,
and commence a
sweep of the area!
[AGENTS gasp]
[AGENT panting]
[JUNICHIRO]
Hm?
[AGENT A]
There he is!
[gasps]
Uh-oh!
[AGENTS panting]
So not cool!
[SUZUNE] 'Scuse me,
have you seen this guy?
[CLERK]
Uh. Oh, Kagami?
He shopped a bit and took off.
I must have just missed
him then. Figures.
This is Yankee One, Suwa.
I have possible visual on
the target inside Oroden.
[FEMALE OPERATOR] The target's
back is turned to the camera,
we can't see his face.
Confirm it, but don't
make a scene.
[JUNICHIRO IMPOSTER]
Huh?
What the--?
Negative!
[YONEKURA] Yankee Two,
Yonekura on the line!
We have eyes on our objective.
[AGENTS grunting]
[JUNICHIRO]
Hm.
[AGENTS gasp]
[JUNICHIRO]
Hmm...
Pardon, may we have a
minute of your time, sir?
No can do, fellas,
I'm in a hurry today.
I insist.
[YONEKURA grunts, gasps]
What the-?
[AGENT C]
He's on the move again!
I've got some bad news!
We came into contact with
the target in Area D6!
Well, miss?
Our cover's blown, this is
no longer a covert op.
I advise granting our agents
permission to detain the target.
[JUNICHIRO] I don't have time
for all this running around
right now; I'm in danger
of being late as it is!
[DINERS, MAIDS chatter]
[MAID A]
Welcome home, master!
Who the heck
were those guys?
[JUNICHIRO] Hm. Bet that
Options girl sent them.
That would explain a lot.
Well, in that case.
There's no reason
for me to hold back.
[KIKUKAWA] Yankee Three,
Kikukawa here.
I have visual on the target.
Cross-reference with the
provided description.
Can you positively
I.D. the subject?
Verification is required.
[KIKUKAWA]
Why the increased caution?
Because we're receiving
multiple reports
of sightings from agents
all over the grid,
and he can't be
everywhere at once.
[MIZOGAMI]
Tango Three, Mizogami.
I have visual in area D2.
[YOSHIOKA] Tango One, Yoshioka!
He's in F1! I repeat, F1!
He's even better
than I expected.
And I expected a lot.
[SUZUNE] Man.
Where the heck could he be?
[SUZUNE] I thought he'd
be due for his fry fix.
Must've beat me there, too.
{GIRL B] We've gotta hurry,
or we'll miss it!
[SUZUNE]
Wait, is that?
[MALE OPERATOR]
What's the status on
the facial recognition system?
[ENGINEER]
It's not good.
As far as I can tell.
The feeds are being
replaced by fakes.
But how?
[ENGINEER] I haven't figured
that out yet, but it looks like.
He's hacking us!
[gasps]
[JUNICHIRO]
There.
Not taking no for an answer is
one thing, but trying to best me
in Akihabara of all places
is like an attack on titan.
With time to spare, too.
I'm off.
[FEMALE OPERATOR] He's breached
all of our firewalls!
[MALE OPERATOR]
Complete system shut down.
He beat us. After everything
we did to find him,
he still managed to
get away from me.
Game well played.
[phone rings]
[gasps]
I finally got a
personalized autograph
from Kanon "Sergeant
Saunders" Hanazawa!
--I could die of happiness!
--I've got you now!
[SUZUNE yells]
[JUNICHIRO gasps]
Well, look at this.
[JUNICHIRO]
Let me out of here!
You can't bag me up like this!
[KOYOMI] Tell me, Suzune, how
did you manage to find him?
I used all of my resources
and came up dry.
I hate to admit it,
but being bested by both
Kagamis wounds my pride.
n
My bro's a shut
with only a few places
he's willing to go, so by
hitting up his usual haunts,
I discovered the
autograph signing.
It's his favorite show,
so I knew he'd come.
How funny. All this time
he was dodging my men
just to get some
girl's silly signature.
[JUNICHIRO] "Silly signature?"
I can't believe you said that!
This is a priceless
treasure to me!
Bura-Kura is gold!
You'd better apologize!
[SUZUNE, JUNICHIRO grunt]
Skipping your meeting like
that was hella rude, jerk!
How about we all just
calm down for a moment?
You know why we are here.
Have you considered the
offer to teach for my school,
Mr. Kagami?
[JUNICHIRO]
I refuse!
Aw, come on!
[JUNICHIRO] In my one month as
a teacher, it became clear to me
that there's a critical flaw
in the education system!
Oh?
[JUNICHIRO]
It takes up too much of my time!
By spending all day
bettering others,
I was worsening my standing
in the anime blog rankings!
[yells]
[JUNICHIRO yelps]
[SUZUNE]
I'm so sorry!
This creature isn't fit
for educating humans!
[KOYOMI] It would appear that
without more drastic measures,
we will never see eye to eye.
[SUZUNE]
Huh?
I think a tour of the academy
grounds will help convince him.
[SUZUNE] You sure you really
want him on your payroll?
Well, I'm going to give
him a trial period.
Before I invite Mr. Kagami to
Hiiragi Academy's main campus,
I want him to get his feet
wet at the Icho branch.
[gasps]
You're joking!
At my school?
Hey! In case you forgot,
I'm right here!
And I'm not taking the job!
We finally arrived!
Welcome to Icho Academy.
Greetings, chairperson.
And what's this?
You brought along some baggage.
Wow, impressive.
We haven't been introduced
and she already hates me.
Thank you for your hospitality.
Would you be willing to
show Mr. Kagami around?
I refuse!
Oh?
[JUNICHIRO, SUZUNE gasp]
[MAKINA]
Of course not!
After all the hard work I put
into finding decent teachers
for this academy only
to have them rejected.
You expect me to be okay
with you hiring some loser?
Alright, what's her deal?
Yeah, uh. She's the
kendo team captain,
a chairperson on the
student discipline board
and she runs the
student council.
Makina Momozono.
[MAKINA grunts]
Are all those titles the reason
she gets to call me a "loser"?
Pretty much. She's Miss
Hiiragi's right hand man.
No one else has more
authority than her.
I read the report; this guy's
a self-indulgent, otaku!
I'll never approve of
this NEET as a teacher.
But Makina. All the teachers
you do approve of are so boring.
So what if they are?
This is about education,
not entertainment!
That is true!
I'm afraid she's got me pegged.
There's no way a person like me
is fit to teach
today's students.
What?
[KOYOMI]
See?
He's amusing, so he's perfect!
He's an unmotivated slacker!
[grunts]
[KIRIKO screams]
[MAKINA grunts]
[gasps]
[thud]
Well that hurt.
[gasps]
I'm so sorry, ma'am! Forgive me.
I got in your way, sorry.
[JUNICHIRO]
Huh.
Why does she look familiar?
[MAKINA] Shouldn't you
be going somewhere?
Yes, ma'am. I was just leaving.
[JUNICHIRO]
What's going on?
This liar's on her way out
because she's been expelled.
[JUNICHIRO]
Huh?
[MAKINA] She's been keeping a
part-time job in secret.
Thought we wouldn't find
out about it, but we did.
That's what she gets.
Man, private schools
sure are rough
if that's all it takes
to get the heave-ho.
It's quite serious.
She was working in a maid café.
She could have at least
gotten hired somewhere
that wouldn't tarnish
the school's image.
[JUNICHIRO]
Hmm.
[grunts]
[JUNICHIRO]
Hey! Tell me, what's the name?
[KIRIKO]
I'm Kiriko Shikishima.
[JUNICHIRO] Not your name,
your maid café's!
Oh, it's called Heart on Heart.
It's in Akihabara.
Have you heard of it?
[JUNICHIRO grunts]
Hmm...
Pick up your stuff
and get back to class.
You're not expelled,
no matter what this
twin-tailed weirdo says.
Excuse me, but you have
no authority on the subject!
And what do you mean
by "twin-tailed weirdo?"
[JUNICHIRO] Actually,
I have every authority.
[KIRIKO]
Uhh...
[JUNICHIRO]
Effective immediately,
I'm a teacher at this school.
[ALL gasp]
[KOYOMI laughs]
[JUNICHIRO] If you
disrespect maid cafés,
then you fail as head
of the student council,
Twin-Tailed Weirdo.
Those two things aren't
even a little bit related.
There's something called
"maid dignity" and
I'm gonna show you.
Prepare yourself for
your first lesson.
[gasps]
[JUNICHIRO]
Hm.
[MAKINA] This is
Makina Momozono speaking.
Don't call me
"Twin-Tailed Weirdo," got it?
In the next episode,
much to my dismay,
I'm forced to work in
a maid café. Just great.
So, uh. Moe, moe.
This is stupid,
I'm not saying it!
Period Four,
"Dignity of Maids."
What the heck does "maid
among maids" even mean?
[MAKINA gasps]
Wait a minute.
Who is this "Razor Girl,"
anyway?