Hey! Don't change that channel!
You don't wanna miss
a second of this one!
You've fallen for
the Mythic rare card?
Koutaro has to play Makina?
I've got two lessons today!
All teachers are looking
for diamonds in the rough,
and I Junichiro Kagami,
the Ultimate Otaku Teacher,
always find them first!
[JUNICHIRO]
Good morning!
Is everybody ready to have
an awesome day? Ha, ha, ha!
Hey! How are you?
Lovely weather!
Yo, what's up? Having fun?
Good! Hey! Hi! Morning! Hello!
[GROUP]
Huh?
[JUNICHIRO]
Hey, guys! Wait up!
Phew!
Check this out.
Sha-bam!
Yeah, whatever.
[JUNICHIRO gasps]
Oh wait, come on!
This beauty is the
Legendary Glorious Dragon!
It's a Mythic rare card that I
won by defeating countless foes.
It's a really big deal!
Fear its wrath!
Now you plebeians,
bow before your king!
Rawr! Rawr! Rawr!
What a freakin' loser.
A grown man obsessed
with a children's game.
They're just pieces
of cardboard, dude.
[JUNICHIRO]
U-Uh... What?
Do you even listen to
yourself when you talk?
You've got a lot to learn!
So, here comes a lesson.
For starters, this is not
just a piece of cardboard!
This card--!
[gasps]
Oh, frak me.
Seems to me like you're the
one who needs a lesson.
So take notes.
You are a teacher.
Part of education is example,
so if you bring a toy to school,
it's going to end up
getting confiscated.
[gasps]
[JUNICHIRO] You're being
hypothetical, right?
You're not! Don't do this!
Stand down!
[yelps]
Idiot.
Well, lesson's over.
You okay, teach?
She really took my
legendary Glorious Dragon.
[SUZUNE]
Why aren't you eating?
I made your favorite meal.
Fried rice omelets!
[sighs]
No, I'm not hungry.
You feelin' okay? You'd tell
me if you were sick, right?
[JUNICHIRO] Yeah, I'm fine.
Just had a bad day at work.
[SUZUNE] Hm? I can't hear
what you're saying.
[sighs]
Man.
That Twin-Tailed weirdo
knows it's important to me!
Why'd she take it?
Mm. Wait. What did Makina take?
My trading card.
The Legendary Glorious Dragon.
Shoulda known!
[JUNICHIRO whimpers]
[MAKINA]
What's wrong?
Why aren't you eating?
[KAZUYA sighs]
I made your favorite meal.
Cheeseburgers.
[KAZUYA]
Oh, uh, right.
It looks great!
You'd tell me if you
were sick, right?
You not feeling
well or something?
Oh, no! I feel good, sis!
Yum! Cheeseburger!
I summon Pact of Moth
which skips your turn.
I cast Morris the Solemn.
Returns him to my hand.
And skips your turn again.
[KAZUYA] C'mon. I can't
even cast a spell!
Inferno. Lose a turn.
[KAZUYA gasps]
My deck's combo.
Flame God's Hammer!
[CROWD gasps]
Whoa!
Let's, play another match!
This time, I'll totally--
[KENJI]
Give me a break.
It doesn't matter what you do,
you'll never beat me!
Yeah, stick to
playing with blocks!
[grunts]
[KAZUYA]
Hm...
[MAKINA gasps]
Oh, shoot.
[gasps]
Huh?
[MAKINA] I forgot I
had this in my pocket.
[gasps]
[KAZUYA] Makina? Do you
know what that is?
No, why? Is it important?
[KAZUYA]
Yeah!
That would explain why
Mr. Kagami made such a big stink
when I took it away from him,
but he really shouldn't have
been showing it
off around school.
He's probably still
crying about it.
[KAZUYA] That's a super rare,
super powerful card
and it just showed
up in my house!
If I could add that
bad boy to my deck,
I might stand a
chance against Kenji!
[KAZUYA] Hey, sis?
Do you mind if I take that?
[MAKINA]
Huh?
I need to borrow it for a while,
but I'll give
it back, I promise!
No. You can't.
I'm only keeping it one night
so he learns he can't
bring his toys to school.
It sounds dumb, but I
know it means a lot to him,
so I'm returning it tomorrow.
As long as he apologizes.
[KAZUYA]
Yeah. Of course.
Sorry, I wasn't thinking.
[door clatters]
[KAZUYA]
I'm leaving!
[MAKINA]
Have a good day!
Watch where you're going!
Don't run! You might trip!
Now...
[gasps]
Where'd the card go?
I know I put it in
my pocket last night!
[gasps] Don't tell me,
Kazuya took it?
[KIDS chatter]
[KAZUYA]
I'm sorry, Makina.
But I need this.
[KAZUYA pants]
[JUNICHIRO]
I, Junichiro Kagami,
despite being a teacher
at Icho Academy,
brought the Legendary Glorious
Dragon from the Magic the Ring
trading card game to school
as a means to show off.
I did this knowing full well it
had nothing to do with class.
I apologize and hereby vow to
never break the rules again.
So, uh. That seemed like a
pretty sincere apology to me.
We'd both truly appreciate it
if you could give
his card back now.
And sorry for the trouble!
[gasps] Would it kill you
to show a little respect?
I acknowledge your apology,
but I can't return your card.
Just give it back already!
No! If you have nothing
else to say. Go!
But... my card.
I think we're done here.
Shouldn't you be
teaching a class?
But, he apologized.
[JUNICHIRO]
You will live to regret this,
Twin-Tailed Weirdo, I swear it.
[MAKINA]
Hmph.
[SUZUNE] I wonder why
Makina's acting so harsh.
It's not like this
is a big deal,
but she's being
really unfair about it.
I swear on Sergeant
Saunders' cannon,
vengeance will be mine!
[ODAWARA]
Mr. Kagami!
Uh.
[SUZUNE]
Hm?
Sorry to interrupt
your tantrum.
I was kinda maybe hoping you'd
help me talk to a girl I like?
[JUNICHIRO groans]
[ODAWARA]
Wait, where are you going?
Are you seriously just going
to ignore me like that?
[JUNICHIRO]
Yes, I am,
I'm in the midst of
plotting my revenge.
And I don't even
know who you are.
Oh, right. Forgot about that.
I'm Joe Odawara from the
class next door to yours.
Don't care.
[ODAWARA] I'm seriously
out of options here.
I want to tell her how I feel,
but I've got a problem.
Sounds real serious, kid.
[ODAWARA]
I'll show you.
Hold onto this
for a second.
[JUNICHIRO] Hm? You just
carry a bucket around?
Hey! How you doin'?
Um. I'm good. Thanks.
[ODAWARA grunts]
Whoa! That is not a natural
reaction to this at all!
You see what I'm
talkin' about?
I can't stop bleeding when
I try to talk to girls.
I just tense up really bad.
That is rough. But considering
I'm not a doctor,
I don't think I'm
qualified to help you.
Well, uh...
All I'd need you to do is pass
along my message for me.
Darn. I guess there's no hope!
[ODAWARA]
Uh! But I'm desperate!
[JUNICHIRO]
I couldn't tell.
But that's not my field
of expertise, so bye!
Man. To be so hard up,
this girl must be special.
Yeah, she is! I mean, not just
anybody can handle being
the head of the
student council!
[JUNICHIRO gasps, pants]
Wait! You're in love
with the Devil?
That changes everything,
my good man!
Listen, while it would be easy
for me to deliver your message,
It wouldn't do you any
good in the long run
without solving your
other problem first.
[JUNICHIRO mocking]
Morning! Thanks for inviting me!
Hey, no problem!
I'm glad you could make it! Ah!
You'd look like you entered
the blood code before going
on the date, which wouldn't
leave the best impression!
You're right. I'm screwed.
Not yet, you're not!
It'll take a little doing,
but I'll get you up and
talking to girls in no time!
I've got a secret weapon!
And here's the cavalry!
[KOUTARO]
Sorry to keep you waiting!
I hurried when I
got your message.
[JUNICHIRO]
It's okay, you're right on time!
This is Koutaro.
Don't let the girly outfit
fool you. He's a boy.
He's the talk of the school,
so I'm well aware.
Um, hello there.
I don't think we've met,
I'm from class two-three.
Nice to meet you.
You can call me Joe.
[JUNICHIRO] Now, what if
we give you a new do?
[KOUTARO]
Why?
[JUNICHIRO]
Just a test!
What kind of test requires
me to have pigtails?
[gasps]
Hey. What are the
two of you up to?
[JUNICHIRO]
Well? Pretty close, huh?
Yeah, if I didn't know better,
I'd think he and
Makina were twins!
What?
[JUNICHIRO] But what we have
here is a boy. Which means?
Right! I'm not bleeding!
Everything's cool!
Wait, back up a sec!
Can you please fill me
in on what's happening?
It's simple!
You're going on a date.
In order to save Joe's heart,
You must become
"Deus Ex Makina!"
I don't get it.
Why me?
[JUNICHIRO]
Koutaro, do you copy?
Roger.
I whipped this baby
up over lunch break.
It's a program that'll get us
through this difficult time.
I call it "Sim Makina!"
All we gotta do is enter
the current scenario
in to this software,
and it will tell us what
course of action to take based
on ol' twin-tails' personality.
'Kay. Let's go.
[JUNICHIRO]
Alright. And we're off!
What would you like to
do first, "Miss Momozono?"
Is there anywhere
you want to go?
You'd better slow your roll!
[ODAWARA]
Huh?
That's some nerve
you've got, punk!
I'm the student council head,
which means you fall in line,
'cause ain't nobody
walking beside me!
That'll get you rubbed out!
Sorry! Won't happen again!
Wait, what?
I don't think she'd really
say things like that.
Yuh-huh!
[sighs]
Well, it's what she's
thinking anyway.
She flaunts her authority to
bend the rules in her favor
while putting down
everyone else around her.
I know firsthand.
[chuckles]
Really? Alright, if you say so.
[KAZUYA]
Hey! Kenji!
I demand we have a
rematch for yesterday!
No way. You're weak and boring.
I'll show you who's weak
and boring, you jerk!
I've got a powerful new
card that'll beat you!
You think one card
is that strong?
[KAZUYA laughs]
Yeah, see for yourself!
Oh, wow!
That thing's super rare!
I never thought I'd
see one for real!
[chuckles]
Sure, what the heck?
A rematch might be kinda fun.
Aw, yeah!
But let's make this one special.
How?
We'll play ante4 style and put
all our cards on the line.
Makes it exciting,
so whaddaya say?
Uh...
[ORANGE HOODIE]
Do it!
[GREEN SHIRT]
What, are you scared?
[KAZUYA]
It'll be alright.
This card's stronger
than anything he has.
There's no way I can lose!
[KENJI chuckles]
Okay!
I hope you're ready for
the fight of your life!
[ODAWARA] I thought this
would be a good place to start.
Strawberry Land is supposed to
be the cutest store in town!
Oh, wow!
I can see why you'd say so!
You've gotta be kidding me!
Huh?
[KOUTARO] Like some stuffed
animals are gonna make me soft.
You must be trippin'!
[yells]
[ODAWARA mummbles]
Sorry. Jeez.
[KOUTARO]
Heh!
Then again, maybe I could use
these poor defenseless animals
to protect my fists
while I'm puttin'
the hurt on some suckas.
Wouldn't want to break
a nail or nothin'.
Hold on, I think your program's
wrong on this one, Mr. Kagami!
I know for a fact Makina
likes cute stuffed animals,
she had them all over her
room when I was visiting.
Those were decoys! They lure
you into a false sense
of security by making
you think she's friendly!
Her villainy
knows no bounds!
That's where she
hides her weapons.
Behind those innocent smiling
faces so no one's the wiser!
[KOUTARO]
He has lost his mind.
[ODAWARA] This is a great
little place if you like pasta.
[KOUTARO]
Sounds great! I'm starving.
[ODAWARA] I'll have
the carbonara, please.
[KOUTARO]
And I would like...
Fresh raw meat!
Don't even cook it,
I wanna see the blood!
[BOTH]
Uh...
[chuckles]
I can't do this!
[JUNICHIRO]
You have to!
Remember, you're not Koutaro,
you're Deus Ex Makina!
Consuming raw meat is the
only way she can suppress
the thirst for the
blood of her enemies!
[KOUTARO]
You're making this up.
[JUNICHIRO]
Oh, no I'm not!
I saw her eating in the
student council room once.
it was like a massacre!
I had no idea.
[SERVER]
Here's your meal.
We had to cook the surface due
to health code regulations.
[KOUTARO laughs nervously]
[JUNICHIRO]
Moment of truth!
Dive face first into your food!
Utensils only slow her down!
She'd never waste a
moment using them!
This is how she
prevents her wild side
from committing
greater acts of evil!
It's a show of restraint!
Now! Unleash the beast within!
[grunts]
[growls]
[gasps]
[MAKINA growls]
[MAKINA] Kazuya better be
prepared for the reprimanding
of a lifetime when he gets home.
[gasps]
Makina, I--
[grunts]
[sobs]
It's time.
You ready for the love
confession simulation?
[KOUTARO]
Yeah.
Tell me something, Joe.
lutter?
Do I send your
heart all
Yeah. You do.
Then get down on your
knees and kiss my kicks
to show me you know
your rightful place.
After that we can
be Facespace official.
[ODAWARA]
Uh?
[grunts]
[ODAWARA sighs]
[gasps]
[chuckles]
[MAKINA] What are you
doing in the bushes?
[JUNICHIRO] I'm supervising.
This foolish boy has been
enchanted by the
siren's song, so to speak.
It's up to me to
break the spell.
His only hope is seeing how
evil that weirdo really is!
[JUNICHIRO yelps]
M-M-M-Makina!
Oh? I didn't know you were
such a good Samaritan.
But I think your mock up
is a little too docile.
[chuckles]
[gasps]
[groans]
[yells]
There can be only one!
[shouts]
[grunts]
[JUNICHIRO]
Hm? Mercy?
Yes, but only this
one time. I need you.
As much as I hate to admit it,
you're the only one who
can help me right now.
Wait. You need help?
Why does that thought scare me
more than getting beat up?
Makina! Hey, I need
to talk to you!
[gasps]
Hi! This may seem sudden,
but... Please go out with me!
[MAKINA]
Uh... What?
[yells]
You creep!
[groans]
Okay... Ow.
[ODAWARA groans]
[JUNICHIRO]
What?!
You lost my mythic rare card?
[KAZUYA sobs]
Aw, man. Well that
explains it. Although.
You should've told me why
you couldn't return it.
I'm sorry. It's my fault.
So, here's what I
need your help with.
[JUNICHIRO]
This ought to be good.
I would like for you
to avenge Kazuya
and get back the
cards in the process.
Huh?
What, did I stutter
just now or something?
Fight this Kenji kid,
win back the cards,
and everything
returns to normal.
No. See, the only card
I care about is mine.
Well, if you don't
play against the kid,
you'll never see it again.
Why does this stuff
always happen to me?
Are you serious?
It's because you're
always doing idiotc things
like bringing your
toys to school!
I refuse! You need to
get it back yourself.
Like a true gamer.
[gasps]
Card games,
video games, board games.
If you lose something playing,
you win it back playing.
That's called "Gamer's Pride"
and it's serious business.
That said. There's no
reason I can't train you.
[JUNICHIRO]
Oh, wow.
You actually have some
pretty good cards!
[KAZUYA]
Yeah, but Kenji's super tough.
It doesn't matter how many times
I try, I just can't beat him.
That's why I stole your
legendary Glorious Dragon card
from Makina. I thought if I
had a card that awesome, I--
You rely too much on stats
and not enough on strats.
[KAZUYA]
What?
I'm saying even the
strongest card is useless
if your strategy doesn't
accommodate its unique
action requirements.
So, whether you sink or swim.
[gasps]
[JUNICHIRO]
Depends entirely on you.
[gasps]
Ya ready? My training
isn't gonna be easy.
[KAZUYA]
Hm!
Okay! It's time to
start the lesson!
Hey. Today's Kazuya's rematch.
Oh yeah?
Let's hope your training pays
off and we can put this to bed.
Thing is, Even the best strategy
depends a little
bit on luck.
But that's what makes
the game so interesting.
What's that mean?
You've just got to be cryptic.
Don't rely on the cards.
It's up to me.
I can do this. I can win.
Let's get this thing
over with. Combat Open!
[JUNICHIRO]
Huh?
He still beat me.
That's alright.
Well, as they say, nothing in
life worth having comes easy.
We'll train some
more after dinner.
Go inside. I'll get
the food started.
[KENJI]
Man, you're really stubborn.
Here! Please, just take it.
I don't wanna battle
you anymore.
It's yours.
I can't. I have to
beat you for it!
[gasps]
[KAZUYA] It won't feel right if
you just give it back to me.
For real? But why not?
'Cause of my
gamer's pride, of course!
[KOUTARO]
Mm...
Okay, looks clear!
Hi, Koutaro!
[yells]
Let's walk home together!
[KOUTARO groans]
[JUNICHIRO]
Hey!
Done for the day?
[ODAWARA]
Let me carry your bag for you!
[KOUTARO] Joe hasn't
stopped asking me out
since he got rejected!
I'm stuck!
[JUNICHIRO]
You'd be a cute couple!
Don't encourage him!
Despite the way I dress,
and that I talk about
cute stuff all the time,
I'm actually not into dudes!
Do something! You're the
one who got me into this!
Sorry, there isn't really
anything I can do about it.
[gasps]
Hey, how'd it go this time?
[KAZUYA chuckles]
Then your lesson's done.
Good job!
[ODAWARA] Koutaro! I
can't live without you!
My life is meaningless--
[KOUTARO]
No means no!
[KAZUYA]
This is Kazuya Momozono,
Makina's little brother!
I finally got Mr. Kagami's
card back, and I even
made friends with Kenji!
Next episode, we meet some
girls who are part of a street
gang and are big fans of the
Fraternal Force Family Rangers!
They say when you're part of a
gang, you're part of a family!
But what about
her real family?
Period nineteen,
"Street Gangs."
t's good for people to
have strong friendships!
I really hope Makina
makes some friends soon.