Hey! Don't change that channel!
You don't wanna miss
a second of this one!
So it's all-out war, huh?
Fighting may not
be my strong point,
but I've got more than
enough tricks up my sleeve!
All teachers are looking for
diamonds in the rough,
and I, Junichiro Kagami,
the Ultimate Otaku Teacher,
always find them first!
[NARRATOR] Activating a
mysterious item left behind
by their father,
five half-siblings
now defend the earth from
the evil forces of Nemesis!
They are...
[FAMILY RANGERS] Fraternal
Force Family Rangers!
[NARRATOR] Fearing that
her twin sister has
succumbed to darkness,
pop idol Nagare Komiya
neglects her own sacred duty!
Thankfully, our hero,
Junichiro Kagami
is there to save the day.
Moved by his act of heroism,
Nagare reveals
a most terrible secret.
Her sister Taki posed
as her at a key audition.
Having won her position
through deceit,
Nagare was convinced that Taki
was the more worthy performer.
Our hero seeks to
prove her wrong,
by throwing her into
a Family Ranger battle!
Nagare performs admirably,
but is soon met with tragedy!
[JUNICHIRO] She's taking
an awful long time to change.
Wonder what's up?
[TAKI]
Hey! Sorry I'm late!
[JUNICHIRO] And now
the real deal shows up.
Didn't expect her so soon.
How did the competition go?
Hold on. Junichiro?
Why are you here?
Oh my gosh, you were
so cool up there, Taki!
Chiyo. Hey.
I know that team meeting
was a big deal for you,
but I'm so glad you got out
early and defended our title!
I felt the
Fraternal Fighting Force
in every note you sang!
What? Is that a joke?
I literally just got here.
Huh?
Uh, so Leader.
Changing the subject, what was
the big meeting about anyway?
Oh, well remember
that dumb jerk
that was picking
a fight with you?
We heard rumors that
he was setting up a posse
to launch a surprise
attack on our gang,
so we wanted to be ready.
Uh-oh. That's not good.
Wait. Would someone
tell me what's going on?
Idol Sister!
[JUNICHIRO panting]
[NAGARE muffled yelling]
[JUNICHIRO] Oh no. What are
you doing? Let her go!
[grunts]
Can it!
Aah!
Let's move, people might see!
Adiós, old man.
[JUNICHIRO]
Ow. That sucked.
[TAKI]
Are you okay?
Nagare competed in
the sing-off instead of me
and she just got kidnapped?
Uh-huh. If I'd known those
guys wanted to attack you,
I wouldn't have planned this.
Either way, this is
out of our league.
We should contact the police!
But if we do that,
it'll cause a huge scandal.
Nagare just got
the lead in that show.
I can't blow it for her.
[JUNICHIRO] The police
won't get the pleasure.
If those punks want to
act like criminal scum.
I'll teach them
a lesson, myself.
As far as they're
concerned, I am the law.
No, seriously,
thanks for kicking my ass
the other day.
I really appreciate it.
That's why I'm definitely
making sure I pay you back.
[MALE OTAKU 21A]
I think that's the car!
Oh hey, you're right!
I hope she's inside!
[MALE OTAKU 21B]
Let's see.
[MALE OTAKU 21A] Whoa!
Aw man, it's really her!
Guess that post was true!
Lady Nemesis and she's so cute!
Uh. What the hell's
going on?
[JUNICHIRO chuckles]
That was too easy.
[TAKI]
I don't get it.
I started a rumor about
a cute Nemesis cosplayer
on the Family Rangers fan site.
They really got into finding her
and the news spread
all over the internet.
[TAKI] Wow, there're witnesses
all over the place.
You can't hide
from me, little punks.
My surveillance network's
got a lock on you
like the eye of Sauron.
[TAKI] You sure
this is the place?
[JUNICHIRO] You can bet your
transformation belt on it.
Well, thank you. I think
I can handle things from here.
All alone?
It's my sister and my problem.
I can't put the other
members of Black Oracle Neo
in danger over this.
[JUNICHIRO] You won't
even tell Face Punch
or Cyborg about this?
I know we used to be friends,
but that's in the past now.
They have their own lives.
Their own places to belong.
They don't need to suffer
because of my mistakes anymore.
I figured. Our leader
sure is a stubborn one.
[THUG 19A] Better play nice
for the camera.
Once your little friends
get a load of you,
they'll come running
straight into our trap,
thinking they're saving
their damsel in distress.
[chuckles]
--[NAGARE] Wait!
--[THUG 19A] Huh?
I am the leader.
I'm the only one you need!
You can do whatever
you want with me,
but leave them out of this!
Oh yeah? Nice.
If you want me that bad,
then I can hardly say no.
[chuckles]
[TAKI] Don't you dare
touch my sister!
Taki! How did you find me?
Never mind that!
I am so mad at you!
[THUG 21B grunts]
Stop it!
[growls]
Wow, so you two
are twins, huh?
Congratulations
on finding us, twerp.
Also, thanks for playing
the hero like a dumb ass
and delivering yourself
right to our doorstep
without anyone to help you.
What're you trying to pull?
Oh, your sister was real nice.
Said I could do
whatever I wanted with her.
[chuckles]
So, with her generous
contribution we're going
to create a little art piece on
camera for everyone to see.
[TAKI] She has nothing to do
with this! Film me instead!
[THUG 19A] Huh? What are
you talking about?
We're going to be filming
both of you, obviously.
[laughs]
Don't you dare!
This isn't funny!
Stop it! Leave her alone!
No!
[ALL gasp]
[SEIJURO]
I think that's enough!
[MINAKO]
Heartless evildoers!
We'll put an end
to your villainy!
Who the hell are you?
[SEIJURO] You kidding me?
What, did you not watch TV
when you were
a kid or somethin'?
[JUNICHIRO] If we're showing up
at a time like this,
then we've got to
be superheroes right?
Huh?
Let's go!
[MINAKO, SEIJURO]
Right!
[MINAKO, SEIJURO, JUNICHIRO]
Family Change!
[SEIJURO] The bonds
we share shall never die!
[MINAKO] The Family Council
has made its decree!
[JUNICHIRO]
Fraternal Force!
[ALL]
Family Rangers!
[JUNICHIRO] This time,
we won't even need the robot!
[THUG 19A]
Family Rangers?
Watch out guys, these nerds
can quote TV shows!
We might all die laughing!
[JUNICHIRO] It's time for the
Family Rangers reunion special.
Sure, we don't have our tights,
but that doesn't mean
we won't win our fights!
--[MINAKO] Let's go!
--[SEIJURO] Roger!
[THUG 21C] You think
that mask gives you powers?
You're nothing but a nerd!
[JUNICHIRO]
Family Blaster!
[yells]
[JUNICHIRO] I'm kidding.
It's just tear gas spray.
You didn't think I was gonna
fight with my fists, did you?
Yeah? You're still
outnumbered!
[gasps]
[THUG 21A, 21B, 21C, 21D groan]
Hold on a sec,
you're Kanou and Nanami
from Black Oracle, aren't you?
[MINAKO]
I'm Family Blue.
[SEIJURO]
Black.
Go to hell!
[MINAKO] Watch your language.
This is a children's show.
But that doesn't mean
we won't rough you up
to save our friends!
[TAKI]
Your friends?
[JUNICHIRO] Ranger teams
need five members, right?
Take it.
[TAKI]
Family Red.
[JUNICHIRO] It's only fair.
You should be red.
Aren't you the leader?
All right, then.
If you insist.
Would you give it
a rest already?
[JUNICHIRO]
More generic goons, huh?
[THUG 19A]
Come here!
[JUNICHIRO]
Not on my watch!
Aye-yai-yai-yai!
[MINAKO, SEIJURO]
Family Double Crash!
[THUG 21E, 21F groan]
[MINAKO] Mr. Kagami,
you and Taki go ahead.
Seijuro and I can handle this!
[JUNICHIRO]
I like it!
[THUG 21A]
C'mon geeks, let's do this.
[SEIJURO] You better
go ahead too, Miss Kanou.
You haven't been in a brawl
in over a year.
You might be rusty.
[MINAKO]
Are you dense or what?
As long as we hold the blade
of justice in our hearts,
it will never rust
and never grow dull.
[SEIJURO] Heh!
I'll take your word for it.
Sword or no sword,
I still gotta keep
in shape for soccer,
so I'm gonna pound
their faces in all the same.
[MINAKO]
Sounds good.
[JUNICHIRO]
Nowhere left to run, pal.
[TAKI]
Give it up and let her go!
[TAKEDA grunts]
I wouldn't move
if I were you.
One little cut and her career
could be ruined for good.
[THUGS chuckle]
What're you gonna
do now, heroes?
Call that giant robot after all?
[yells]
[JUNICHIRO]
Family Blaster!
Aah!
Uuh.
[JUNICHIRO]
Well, so much for that.
[chuckles nervously]
[laughs]
The girls can wait
'cause I'm sick of you
and your damn mouth.
Spouting all this hero crap.
Let's see if you're
still such a smart ass
after I cut open
your freakin' face!
Junichiro!
Family Dynamic secret weapon.
A low-profile,
stainless-steel wire whip.
[TAKEDA groans]
[JUNICHIRO] Every proper hero
has an ace up their sleeve.
They don't show
their true strength
'til the odds are
against them. Now you know.
[TAKEDA growls]
What, you think this is over?
I can kick your
pathetic ass any time
and any place I like!
I'll hunt you down
and make every day
of your life a living hell!
[JUNICHIRO]
Hmmm.
If you're gonna keep
tossing out boomerangs,
you have to be ready when
they come flying back at you.
Consider that a free lesson.
Boomerangs?
Something's happening!
Look outside!
[THUG 19A]
Huh?
Ah!
[THUG 21B]
This is messed up!
There's like,
hundreds of people out there!
All of my friends
from Black Oracle Neo
and everyone from
the Family Rangers fan group.
Whoa. Even the Rock Rangers
groupies are here.
I said this was a
reunion special, didn't I?
And when they do those,
it turns into a crossover
with the new rangers, too.
And spoiler alert,
the villains never
make it out on top.
Anyway, since you guys
are a little slow
on the uptake, let me lay out
the scenario for you.
The people outside think we're
having a friendly after-party.
In other words,
they don't know a thing
about your dastardly
deeds from earlier.
[chuckles]
And if all those people
did find out,
what do you think
they'd do to you?
Mr. Toshihiko Takeda?
Hold up,
how do you know my name?
Not just you. I know all of
your friends names, too!
Like Yukito Date here,
Hitoshi Imagawa,
Hideyuki Konishi,
and Haruto Uesugi.
Also, this is
kind of villain 101,
but if you're going to
kidnap someone,
maybe don't use
your parent's car.
Actually, just don't
kidnap anyone at all,
because in this day and age,
it's easy to
look people up online.
Now, the next question.
Tell me, whose life is about
to become a living hell?
It's not mine.
[chuckles nervously]
We never got behind
this idea much, ourselves.
We sorta got
dragged into it, y'know?
[THUG 21B] Yeah, I'm like, uh,
actually glad you stopped him.
I mean, kidnapping?
Way not cool, right?
But hey, all's well
that ends well.
Peer pressure is bad, yo.
[THUG 21C]
Later, Take.
[THUG 21B]
Yeah, it's getting late.
Hey, get back here!
You guys were totally
into this before!
[JUNICHIRO] So, uh. Not telling
you how to live your life,
but now might be a good time
to cut your losses
before things get really ugly.
Mr. Kagami, are you okay?
[JUNICHIRO]
Peachy.
[TAKEDA grunts]
It's your fault!
It's all your fault!
[TAKEDA yells]
Taki!
No!
She's fine. It was
just a scratch.
Uh--that's not the problem.
[NAGARE snarls, yells]
--[JUNICHIRO gasps]
--[MINAKO] Ehhh.
How dare you.
[TAKEDA yells]
[CROWD MAN 21A]
What was that?
Dude! That guy
just flew out the window!
So funny thing,
we used to call Nagare
"The Dragon" back in the day.
And it's not just 'cause
the "Ryu" in "Komi-ryu"
means "dragon." The truth is,
if you lay a hand
on her sister, it awakens
a dragon's wrath within her
that will shake the heavens!
Hell no. Screw this.
I already lost
to one little girl.
That's more than enough!
Fraternal Strike!
Family Final Dragon Crush!
[MINAKO] Once the dragon
is unleashed,
her fury is so powerful,
not even Seijuro can stop her.
[MAN 21B] That was
a killer performance!
[MAN 21C]
It felt so real!
Huh? Ah!
Are you kidding?
If she could've
done that all along,
she didn't need us
to rescue her!
[NAGARE] I guess the after-party
idea turned into a real thing.
[TAKI]
Yeah.
--[NAGARE] Taki, um.
--[TAKI] Hmm?
Since we're here,
I wanted to talk to you
about Black Oracle Neo.
[TAKI]
Mm.
It's kind of awkward
to ask this,
but do you think
I could join, too?
Huh? Uh, yeah.
That would be fine
with me. I guess.
But I'm kinda confused here,
I thought you wanted me
to quit the whole gang thing.
[NAGARE] It's fine. I finally
know where both of us belong,
and I'd like for that
to be together again.
[NAGARE]
Mr. Kagami!
That's great, but now
I'm even more confused.
Oh yeah?
Seems clear to me that
she received a lesson
from Mr. Kagami.
Okay, and that's a good thing?
Yep. It was
for me, at least.
He really helped me
pull it together
after I disbanded the group.
And he wasn't even
my teacher at the time.
I know this might
sound cheesy,
but it's like he has
this weird gravity about him.
You made a ranger team...
[MINAKO] He finds your
true self, hidden away
and pulls it out
of your heart.
It didn't seem like
it was your scene.
And you know
how these things go.
Five is the magic number
for teams on TV.
Just the primary colors!
No, they added gold
and silver later!
Oh yeah, after
the halfway point
they had support members, huh?
I thought you were a fan!
That really didn't occur to you?
Even if things
got a little messy here,
everything is more fun
with friends.
I don't know if the word
"friends" is appropriate
since it's more like Black
Oracle Neo and a bunch of
Family Rangers fans
kind of mashed together.
--Exactly.
--Huh?
[MINAKO] We all took one of
Mr. Kagami's lessons,
so we're all friends now!
[TAKI gasps]
Hey there, Leader.
You diggin' the party?
Oh, uh, sure.
But I was thinking.
Things should change.
It's been long enough for me.
Maybe I should go
back to school next year.
[chuckles]
--Don't bother.
--Huh?
The whole "streets
are my school" thing is like,
half of your character!
If you give that way
of thinking up, what are you?
We've got more than
enough schoolgirls!
Frankly, things are
a little crowded,
so it's getting harder
and harder to stand out.
And these students
aren't normal, by the way.
They're all over the top and
they're all fighting to maintain
their individuality in a cast
that's constantly expanding!
Just kidding.
You'll stand out on your own
just fine, wherever you go.
I'll be waiting to see you
in class, Leader.
[giggles]
Count on it.
[NAGARE] Well, what
an interesting turn of events!
I suppose I'll just
have to apply for
Icho Academy next year!
Huh? For real?
I won't stop you
from doing what you want,
but that certainly
doesn't mean
you get to do everything
I want without me.
[TAKI] Whoa, wait.
What does that mean?
[JUNICHIRO] Fighting again? You
need another lesson already?
[TAKI]
No, I'm fine.
[NAGARE] Good! Then it looks
like we'll be classmates soon!
[TAKI]
Come on!
It was the biggest fart ever
and then just like magic...
[JUNICHIRO]
Pardon me, gents.
What are you up to
this fine day?
Not goin' to school.
So get lost.
I'm not here as an educator.
Think of me as a headhunter
for Black Oracle Neo.
Look, guys,
if you're gonna loiter,
why not expand
your loitering horizons?
Join a cool team
and you can pursue
the ultimate loitering
with some friends.
[MAKINA] Surely my ears
are deceiving me.
[JUNICHIRO]
Uh oh.
[MAKINA]
Please tell me you are not
recruiting for a gang!
Oh, why, hello there.
You've got it all wrong.
I mean, how much did you hear?
Can we talk this over?
I'm through with talking!
Now is the time for justice.
Swift and brutal
and aimed directly at you!
Also, if you don't
take off those glasses...
[JUNICHIRO]
Please! Mercy!
[MAKINA, JUNICHIRO
indistinctive yelling]
Next year. New school.
New friends.
Heh. Bring it on.
[TAKI] I'm not losing
to you, or anyone else!
[YAMATO]
A pleasure to meet you.
I'm Yamato Toune, a former
classmate of Junichiro's.
In case you were wondering,
he's always been
an incurable Family Rangers fan.
Next episode,
we find out what Junichiro
really yearns to do.
Because I have a feeling it
isn't teaching at this school.
At least I hope not, because my
lab could really use his genius!
Period twenty-two,
"Castle Junichiro."
I think it's time
we finally finish that
Anywhere Door of yours.