Hey! Don't change that channel!
You don't wanna miss
a second of this one!
The one distressing our damsel
is the King of Games himself!
I have no choice but to
face him on his own turf!
All teachers are looking
for diamonds in the rough,
and I Junichiro Kagami,
the Ultimate Otaku Teacher,
always find them first!
[JUNICHIRO] I didn't
think hostile takeovers
and political marriages
actually happened in real life.
It's kinda cool when you
look at it that way.
And yet that doesn't make
me feel any better about it.
Which really is unfortunate.
Could be a favorable marriage
if you were more into him.
Then again, the guy
doesn't strike me
as the "prince charming" type.
I can't blame you for
wanting to run away.
Wait.
How much do you know about him?
Well, other than he's the
CEO of Activision Frigate?
Enough. His father was
the founder of Macrosoft,
and for three years running he's
been the undisputed champion
of the King Halo series.
He's a genius programmer
despite his age,
and his name is Hell Gates.
'Kay, you've done
your homework.
But that also means you
know what the odds are.
There's no way you can stand
against a force like that.
Hey now, don't get
melodramatic on me.
He's just a dude,
it's not like we're
fighting the Ultima Weapon.
[CROWD cheers]
[MALE CUSTOMER A]
I can't believe it!
He really beat the
game with just a knife!
This guy looks a lot
like Hell Gates, right?
[CROWD chatters]
[CROWD gasps]
[MALE CUSTOMER A]
No way! It is him!
[chattering continues]
[EMPLOYEEnA]
Excuse, me! Sir?
You've earned a prize for
getting today's high score.
I know it isn't a big deal,
but, Here's your medal.
[gasps]
Sorry. You probably
don't even care.
[gasps]
Of course I do. It's a
credit to my greatness.
Thanks for the memories.
[MADOKA]
Aw, I didn't sleep a wink.
Hey! Mornin'!
Want something for breakfast?
No. I should really get--
[yelps]
[MADOKA] How in the
world did he find me?
What are you doing here, Gates?!
Oh. Come on.
You know the answer to that one.
Now that you've
turned sixteen,
it's not creepy or weird
for me to marry you, right?
I wasn't sure about him,
but once he said he's
your fiancé, I let him in.
Caught yourself one of
those rich handsome types.
Way to go, girl!
Let's step outside, Gates.
I need some air.
What in the hell is
the matter with you?
The announcement
of our engagement
isn't for a whole other week!
I'm free until then!
[GATES] What difference
does a measly week make?
The end result is still the same
whether there are
seven days or zero.
[sighs]
Let's just cut to the chase
and live happily ever after.
I mean, if I'm buying your small
business that I don't want,
there had better be a perk
in there for me somewhere.
[gasps]
I'm doing you a favor.
Just think of all
your employees.
Now they get to be part of
a real company. Big time.
[BOTH grunt]
Sorry, I seem to have spilt
my water all over your head.
'Sup, King of Games?
Mr. Kagami, how long
have you been there?
Madoka.
Please don't tell me this
eccentric soon-to-be-dead man
is an acquaintance of yours.
Uh. Yes... You see, he's my...
Real fiancé.
Nice to meetcha.
I see.
Y'know, I'm a pretty
big gamer myself.
That's what made Madoka
fall in love with me!
'Cause I got mad game, yo!
Wait. What?
Like there's any chance
I'm gonna believe you.
If that were true,
I'd have had her hot and
bothered a long-- Uh...
I'm sure.
After you got so excited
winning just one of these.
[grunts]
Your triumph was
totally trending.
[grunts]
Last night, as we stood on the
balcony underneath the stars,
She gazed into my eyes and said,
"There's no way I'd marry a man
who'd buy a company
he has no interest in!"
And then, we decided
to run away together!
Wait!
That's how you remember it?
A rival.
Will you tell me your name?
Sure.
Junichiro Kagami.
[GATES]
Junichiro!
I hereby challenge
you to a duel!
Heh!
Nah, I refuse.
[GATES] Hmph. Alright,
so here's what we're gonna do.
Wait! Whaddaya mean you refuse?
I just don't see the point
when the results are
painfully obvious.
Why waste my time?
[GATES]
Why you arrogant--!
But maybe if we
raise the stakes.
[gasps]
I'll agree to duel you
under the condition that,
when I win, you cancel
your engagement to Madoka.
Oh, plus. You give up on
the company buyout thing.
[gasps]
[MADOKA]
So that's what you're up to.
I'll tell you what.
In the interest of fairness,
why don't we play King Halo?
Seeing as your company makes it,
you might even stand
a chance against me.
Are you serious, or just insane?
In fact.
Why don't we play the version
that hasn't been released yet?
Y'know, the one coming
out next month?
King Halo 3.
That way, you get an edge
and I get a chance to literally
beat you at your own game.
Obviously, if I win,
you will have to forfeit
your own pursuits of Madoka.
However, there's something
else I want, too.
For my second condition,
once I've beaten you,
you must never touch
another video game for
as long as you live.
[gasps]
Fine.
It'll be more fun this way.
I accept your terms.
[chuckles]
Sure about that?
I always make good
on my promises.
I will collect on this bet.
What do you mean
by that? Tell me.
When this is all done,
he'll be hopping on a boat.
Once the ferry
reaches the U.S.,
he'll spend the rest of his
life under twenty-four hour
surveillance by my company.
That way I'll know he's
abiding by our agreement.
But, doesn't that
seem like overkill?
It's just a game.
it isn't worth it!
[JUNICHIRO]
Sure it is!
After all, what's the point
in facing the King of Games
if there's no risk of ending up
in the Home For Infinite Losers?
You'll get no
argument from me.
No! Don't do this!
[chuckles]
Then our duel will take
place this evening.
Hope you're ready.
Our venue...
...Is Tokyo Treasureland!
What?!
Come on!
I can't believe you made another
stupid promise like that!
But I'm not gonna lose.
Who cares?
Haven't you heard
the expression
about pride coming
before a fall?
[MADOKA] Listen.
You're better off giving up
and forgettin' about this.
I'm the daughter
of an entrepreneur,
so I have responsibilities
to the family business,
but none of that involves you.
It's just my time to start
acting like a grownup.
Man. With a speech like that,
I almost believed you.
[grunts]
[JUNICHIRO] How about you stop
acting like the daughter of KMC,
and start acting
like a teenager?
Once you're back
to your old self,
tell me again what
you want to do.
[gasps]
What I really want is
to achieve my dream.
To work with the man I love to
make our company successful.
That doesn't include
a company takeover.
Especially if it
includes a marriage
to someone I don't
love let alone like.
I can't stand the thought.
Then you need to sit back
and let me do my thing.
Part of being a grownup is
giving kids what they want.
Leave it to me.
[MADOKA] Shouldn't you
be taking your lunch break
right about now?
Nah, we've got more important
business to attend to.
Like preparing for
tonight's fight!
But I need help,
and the only one who can
provide it is right here.
[KISAKI]
Hm? What's up, Junichiro?
You got a second?
I need a favor.
[STUDENTS chatter]
[KISAKI]
Interesting!
Talk about blood
boiling material.
But, yeah, I can teach you.
I've played quite
a bit of King--
Oh, no.
I don't need training.
I need to borrow a console.
[KIRIKO] Mr. Kagami called
asking for my help!
[KANAN]
Why would he call you--
[KIRIKO]
Just go away!
[BOTH gasp]
Well that was weird.
[JUNICHIRO] So that about
covers the basics.
Other than that,
do whatever you want.
Sure!
--Sounds fun.
Okay, then! Let's fight.
Can they really help you train?
[JUNICHIRO]
Huh?
[KISAKI] It's just they
don't seem too aware
of what they're doing.
We're having a hard time
believing they're
good at this game.
They're not.
In fact, they've never
even played it before.
[KISAKI] Are you for real?
There's no way you're gonna get
enough practice
against amateurs.
On the contrary, amateurs are
exactly what I need.
[KANAN]
We can work together for now,
but you're not
gonna drag me down.
This is for Mr. Kagami, so you'd
better pull your weight!
[KIRIKO gasps] I liked you
better when you didn't talk.
[KANAN]
Okay. I see the enemy.
I just have to get
closer to him now.
[KANAN]
Oh, how do I run again?
I-I think it was this button?
[KANAN groans]
[KIRIKO] So is that what
you were going for?
[KANAN] It's a lot
harder than it looks!
I don't see you doing anything!
[KIRIKO laughs] It's literally
just using a joystick to walk.
I think I'll be fine,
thank you very much.
Besides, I do harder
stunts as Ra--
Whoops, silly me.
I almost let out a secret!
[giggles]
[JUNICHIRO] She can't seriously
believe her identity as
Razor Girl is still a mystery
to her classmates, right?
I mean, it's not like she
wears a mask or anything.
[KIRIKO]
Here comes the pain!
[KIRIKO yells]
[KIRIKO groans]
[KANAN]
Oh, my! Are you motion sick?
And after all the talk about
the hard stunts you do, too.
You can't help
Mr. Kagami like that.
Guess you're not the Hot Potato
you thought you were.
[laughs]
[yelps]
[KIRIKO]
Sorry. My finger slipped.
[KANAN grunts]
Oops!
I don't know what any
of these buttons do!
[KIRIKO]
Oh, no! I slipped again!
Sorry, I was trying
to bring up the map
and I pulled the
trigger on accident!
So, at this rate, there's
no way either one of them
will come over here
to fight you.
Are you sure this
is good practice?
I'm gonna go give
'em some pointers.
No. Don't.
[bickering continues]
They're doing fine.
It's exactly what
I wanted to see.
[CUSTOMER A] This thing's
about to start, right?
[CUSTOMER B]
Should be.
[CROWD chatters]
[CUSTOMER C]
There's Hell Gates!
I can't believe the King Halo
World Champion is really here!
You think I'd look cool
if I wore shades like him?
[GATES] Hm! I see the King
Halo 3 cabinets arrived.
But it's not too late to
pick a different game.
No, I want to
dethrone you at this.
Then our match style
will be Team Battle,
one player commanding
ten NPCs per side.
[STUDENTS sigh]
Hey, Madoka! I hope
you've packed your bags.
We'll be leaving for the
U.S. right after this.
[groans]
Alright. It's time
to start the lesson!
[CROWD cheers]
[GATES] Two enemies
at my eleven o'clock.
Both out of range.
Alright. Primary weapon
change from Plasma Pistol
to Beam Assault Rifle.
The champ is
making his move!
This looks bad.
Quit fooling around.
Your allied forces
are dwindling!
You need to get your
head in the game!
[MADOKA]
What in the world?
Why is he playing like
Kiriko and Kanan?
[GATES]
Finally found you, Junichiro!
I think it's about time
I humbled your bundle!
Heh.
[gasps]
[GATES]
What the heck is going on?
I didn't write any code
for weapon vanishing.
That isn't supposed to happen!
[JUNICHIRO]
"I am Error."
[GATES gasps]
Unreleased software tends
to have glitches like this
when the user
behaves unexpectedly.
I'm surprised you don't
have a workaround.
Maybe you're not such a
genius programmer after all.
[gasps]
[GATES]
What's going on with my legs?
I can't move my character!
[gasps]
[JUNICHIRO]
Isn't there a saying,
"all's fair in love and war"?
How appropriate.
This match is crazy.
So many bugs!
But, why?
By performing in-game actions
inspired by amateurs,
he's able to exploit
vulnerabilities in the code.
Talk about dirty.
I've never seen
anything like it.
Of course not. No one has.
Because there's no way to
predict what he's going to do.
It's a fact of life when
dealing with Junichiro.
[JUNICHIRO gasps]
[JUNICHIRO] Looks like
I'm not immune to it myself.
Guess it's time for Plan B!
[GATES]
Where are you going?
[GATES gasps]
[GATES]
The heck did that come from?
There's no way.
The buildings on this
map are just obstacles,
you shouldn't be
able to enter them!
[JUNICHIRO]
Thanks to the glitch,
I was able to clip
myself up here.
Think of it as a higher
plane of existence.
Like you're enlightened?
Gimme a break.
You're just standing in a
weird place, that's all!
[GATES]
You think I can't snipe you?
[gasps]
What? I'm still bugged?
Why didn't your gun
disappear this time?
[JUNICHIRO]
"Higher plane of existence."
That lower area is
overrun with errors now,
making it a no-guns zone.
But I'm literally on
a different plane.
And up here, I have the
full right to bear arms!
[GATES grunts]
[growls]
[GATES]
Little punk!
[JUNICHIRO] I've done
a lot of QA testing
for different video game
companies in the past.
[grunts]
[JUNICHIRO] And if I learned one
thing from that experience,
you have to be
prepared for anything.
Because you never know
what's going to happen
when the game breaks around you.
[gasps]
[JUNICHIRO] But I'm guessing
that wasn't in your manual.
Was it, your highness?
[laser shot]
[JUNICHIRO]
Boom. Winning.
I can't believe this happened.
But a duel is a duel.
I will accept my
defeat like a man.
I'm abandoning KMC
per your terms.
[gasps]
However...
I demand we have a rematch.
This time on King Halo 2.
The version both of
us have mastered.
Where nothing can hold us back.
No bugs or glitches.
This round will be
decided solely on skill.
Put your honor as a
gamer on the line.
[JUNICHIRO]
Hm. Nah, I'm going home.
As I expected.
I knew you couldn't be
content with such a cheap--
Wait, you're leaving?!
Yeah, of course I am.
I got what I wanted.
And besides, Cased Closed
is coming on. Bye.
Hold on!
I can't end things this way.
Not until I've proven
to everyone here
my FPS skills are
superior to yours.
I'll show you why
I'm the world champ.
[sighs]
You're worse than Hercule.
Okay, fine.
[GATES]
I'm ready for him now.
Doesn't matter what kind
of tricks he tries to pull.
[GATES]
What?!
Sniper! Fan out, and find him!
[GATES grunts]
He's destroyed half my NPCs!
Where is his fire coming from?
[grunts]
There's no way he's
already got a lock on me!
[GATES]
I can't let him pin me down!
[GASPS grunts]
[GATES scoffs]
He's toying with me.
This is bad.
Gotta hurry and take
control of this fight!
[gasps]
[GATES]
He's predicted everything.
My moves, the NPCs,
he had it all figured out!
[GATES]
He's in a league all his own!
I'm the king and this peasant
is about to dethrone me
without breaking a sweat!
[GATES]
But it isn't over yet.
I became the King of
Games for a reason.
And I won't let him
shame my title!
[GATES] It's time we
finished this, Junichiro!
[GATES yells]
[JUNICHIRO] Discarding his
armor to increase his speed.
That's a smart call
given his situation.
With guts and quick
thinking like that,
it's no wonder he
became a champion.
[grunts]
[gasps]
[JUNICHIRO] You're good, but you
still get the red ring of death.
[gasps]
Y'know, I tried to
do you a favor.
By beating you with glitches,
you had the benefit of the doubt
that I wasn't as skilled as you.
I didn't see that.
I admit defeat.
[CROWD cheers]
[CUSTOMER A]
Flawless victory!
[ALL cheering]
Junichiro.
I have to admit. I am
impressed by your skills.
Why haven't I ever seen you
compete in a tournament?
Why? Because I don't think
games are for competition.
They're for having fun.
Makes sense.
[MADOKA]
Hey, Gates!
[GATES]
Hm?
[MADOKA] He won fair and square,
so don't act like a sore loser!
That's hurtful. I told him
he's the better player.
[MADOKA] Wait.
You aren't mad he beat you?
No. I'm not.
Actually, I'm happy about it,
because now the woman I love
can be with a man
of her choosing.
Now I think I want
you even more.
How about that?
[gasps]
Hold on! You said you
were giving up on me!
Now you're not?
I agreed to give up on
the political marriage,
but I'll never quit trying
to win your heart.
Oh. What am I gonna do?
[SUZUNE] Y'know,
seeing them like this
makes me think they'd
be a cute couple.
And that concludes
today's lesson.
Y'know what?
Even though he's my rival,
I don't know a thing about him.
How did you meet
this guy, anyway?
Well, he's a teacher.
The most interesting
one at my school.
[JUNICHIRO] So I'm guessing you
met Gates in a random encounter?
[MADOKA] Sort of. At the
big Game Expo last year,
he was running his mouth
about how the Japanese
industry is doomed.
I gave him a piece of my mind
and then he started
talking about
"needing me so he can
become a true king."
So weird.
Who knows what he meant?
Guy's nuts.
Well, it makes
perfect sense to me.
Everyone he knows just tells
him what he wants to hear,
but you were honest with him.
[MADOKA gasps]
[JUNICHIRO] A person who
can do something like that
when no one else will is
worth their weight in gold.
And when you find that person,
you'll do anything you possibly
can to be with them.
[MADOKA]
Hey, uh.
Do you know what it was that
made me fall in love with you?
[JUNICHIRO]
No?
I had gotten pretty curious
about how much you were worth.
Being a famous
troublemaker and all.
Come to find out...
I couldn't see your number.
That was a first for me.
I didn't know what
it was at the time,
but something about
you is... priceless.
[JUNICHIRO]
Hm?
[BOTH grunt]
Hey!
[MADOKA]
So you're right,
I'll do anything I can to be
with you, until you marry me.
That's my goal.
You're stuck with me,
like it or not!
[JUNICHIRO whimpers]
Bye, darlin'.
See you later!
[chuckles]
[GATES] This is the
genius programmer
and King of Games, Hell Gates!
I'm sure you've heard of me.
Junichiro. You could be so
much more than a teacher,
why waste your potential?
Next episode, my rival
has to clean up
a sealed-off boarding
house within the school.
And weird things happen
the whole time.
[GATES yells] Period sixteen,
"Take Me to the Afterlife."
As if a CEO's daughter
wasn't enough,
now there's this ghost girl?
Guess being a teacher
isn't that easy.