[JUNICHIRO]
I have YD.
You've never heard of it?
What?
I like wearing
yukata on dates?
Or yummy dinners?
Wrong!
It's a debilitating illness.
where you can only do
what you yearn to do.
I'm the chairperson
of Hiiragi Academy,
Koyomi Hiiragi,
And I am here today
to recruit you.
[JUNICHIRO] Not taking no
for an answer is one thing,
but trying to best me in
Akihabara of all places,
is like an attack on titan.
[KIRIKO screams]
[gasps]
[JUNICHIRO]
You're not expelled,
no matter what this
twin-tailed weirdo says.
Prepare to be schooled.
[MAKINA] "Maid dignity"
are you serious?
[JUNICHIRO] Of course!
This is her way of life.
Until you understand that,
you have no right to expel her.
[MAKINA scoffs]
The modern concept of a maid
began in the 19th century.
Domestic service was the second
largest source of employment
in Victorian England, where they
served as symbols of wealth.
There were about
17 types of maids,
ranging from Housekeepers
to Step Girls.
The so called "maids"
at these cafes you like so
much are just fetish bait.
They have precious little
to do with the originals.
I figured you'd say that.
Sorry, but you're way off.
Well. If you're so smart,
then please. Explain it to me.
[JUNICHIRO]
Hm. Are you sure?
[gasps]
You realize you're
agreeing to a battle.
If I can teach you about maids,
then you have to
admit I'm a teacher.
[gasps]
The philosophy of this
school is to learn,
think, and devise
your own answers.
Only then can your spirit
experience true
richness and growth.
Maids have no dignity, okay?
At least the trashy ones
you're talking about don't!
Working that kind of job is
against our schools' principles,
and I don't need you, of all
people, to teach me that!
[KIRIKO gasps]
[JUNICHIRO]
Hm.
[KOYOMI]
Are you certain?
[gasps]
You can make that
bold assessment
without even seeing the cafe?
You're that sure?
Well, it's obvious.
Oh, is it?
[sighs]
Good. Then let's go.
[ALL]
Welcome home, master.
And welcome home,
milady as well!
[JUNICHIRO giggles]
Why am I here?
Okay, off to work for me.
[MINAMI]
Kagamin!
[MINAMI giggles]
Whoa, what the--?
You're back!
Oh, hi there, Manager.
The manager?
That little girl?
You've been here before?
And so often she knows you?
[gasps]
Once or twice.
Kagamin is our number one
platinum VIP customer!
He set a record by visiting
50 times in one month!
Why, in fact, he was
just here this morning!
[SUZUNE]
I see!
So you've just been here feeding
your addiction to maids, huh?
Uh, no!
If you look, this particular
café has a school motif!
I was training for work!
Liar!
[growls]
[JUNICHIRO, SUZUNE grunting]
Such a loving family.
[MAKINA gasps]
[JUNICHIRO]
Anyway, back on topic.
Yes, as I was trying to say,
this is the manager of
"Heart on Heart" Maid Café.
She looks young, but she
graduated with me,
then took a trip to England
to study the history of maids.
Neat, huh?
Minami Kitayama, 17 years old!
[MAKINA, SUZUNE]
Uh...
[KOYOMI]
Hm...
17 years old.
[JUNICHIRO]
Now that introductions
are out of the way,
I actually have a favor to ask.
Uh-huh?
[JUNICHIRO] Can you let
the Twin-Tailed Weirdo
over there work as one of
your maids for the day?
Huh? I didn't agree to that!
[JUNICHIRO]
It's the only way to learn.
You have to experience the true
dignity of a maid firsthand.
[SUZUNE]
Huh?
If you can't do it alone,
I'm sure my sister would be
more than happy to join you.
I'd rather not!
Should be easy, right?
No! I mean, it's stupid!
Would you back me up, Koyomi?
Please?
[giggles]
[gasps]
[bell rings]
[MINAMI]
This is a special announcement
for our lords and
ladies who are at home,
but also at school somehow.
Today, we have two new maids
entering our mansion-slash
school-slash café!
Makkie on the left and
Suzu on the right!
--[CROWD cheers]
--[BOTH giggle nervously]
Not that I'm complaining,
mind you, but why'd
you agree to my idea
when you knew this was going to
be absolute torture for her?
It's obvious.
I'll take any excuse to
make her lose her cool.
--Just look at that face.
--[MAKINA giggles nervouly]
Huh. I see.
[MAKINA] Sorry to keep
you waiting. Master.
[gasps]
Here's your giant-size
order of French fries.
Let me know if you
need anything else.
[JUNICHIRO] Actually, I do.
[gasps]
These fries are
missing something.
You forgot to cast the
deliciousness spell.
[gasps]
The what?
[JUNICHIRO]
Watch her, she's a pro.
[MAKINA]
Kiriko?
Nummy yummy, nummy yummy,
moe moe kyun!
[giggles]
[gasps]
[MAKINA whimpers]
[JUNICHIRO]
That's a Bingo.
I have to do that?
It's so dumb!
Really need my spell here.
[gasps]
I'm waiting!
[whines]
No!
[JUNICHIRO]
Hm.
Not so tough now,
are you Twin-Tailed Weirdo?
[gasps]
You brought your fries?
Of course I did,
Kiriko cast a spell on them,
so they're super good.
She's the fry queen.
Maybe I should start
calling her "Potatoes."
So stupid.
What does that have to
do with maids, anyway?
Moe moe kyun!
I am not engaging
in that nonsense.
Fine. So you're a crappy maid.
But I hope you're
proud of yourself,
expelling an awesome student
who can do something you
can't even dream of doing.
[gasps]
You're boring.
Totally one-dimensional.
It's a shame, too, since Options
is an interesting character,
but her arc won't last two
episodes with a sidekick
like you dragging her down.
[MAKINA]
Stop right there.
[JUNICHIRO]
Hm?
[MAKINA] I was just taking
a break, that's all.
Makina Momozono
doesn't quit that easily.
[MAKINA]
Now excuse me.
All fired up. I like it.
Guess she's ready.
Catchphrase time.
Okay, time to
start the lesson.
[PATRON B chuckles]
[KIRIKO, MAKINA]
Have a safe journey!
[PATRON B]
See ya later, girls.
[KIRIKO giggles]
You don't have to be so tense!
Have fun with it.
[MAKINA]
Uh?
As long as the master or
mistress enjoy themselves,
we can do whatever we want!
There are no rules here,
so get creative!
[MAKINA]
Uh... Huh.
Sorry to keep you waiting.
Oh, wow!
[PATRON C]
Look at that, a rice omelet!
Isn't that your
favorite, Takeshi?
Mmhmm, yeah!
[gasps] Just a moment please,
young master. Here.
[BOY A]
Uh, huh?
[MAKINA chuckles]
[BOY A gasps]
Awesome!
My pleasure, master.
[BOY A]
That's so cool.
I almost don't wanna eat it now!
I'm glad you like it.
I'm happy to serve.
Yeah, yeah.
You learned one little trick.
Don't act like you're a pro
all of a sudden, okay?
I wasn't thinking that.
[JUNICHIRO] The "name on the
omelet" thing is like, Maid 101.
[MAKINA gasps]
[JUNICHIRO] My sister's
leveled up to pictures.
[BOYS laugh]
[MAKINA whines]
Now, watch a real pro at work.
[gasps]
[KIRIKO giggles]
All done!
You wanted something
like this, right?
[PATRON D gasps]
Perfect! It's art!
[growls]
And that's not all.
Every master and every mistress
has their own demands.
Their own little quirks
and their own secret key
to unlock their smile.
You have to understand them
before you can make them happy.
Are you kidding?
Just look for yourself.
[MAKINA gasps]
I'd like... some orange juice.
Huh? For real?
I-I mean it doesn't have to
be orange juice, I guess.
[MINAMI huffs]
Whatever.
Can... I get a cup?
Uh, if you're gonna
be picky. Fine.
Huh? I'm supposed
to drink with this?
You've got some attitude!
Here!
I guess I'll have to learn
to deal with this somehow.
That's gotta be the
worst service ever.
You're wrong.
Look again.
[MAKINA]
Huh?
[JUNICHIRO] That customer of
hers has never been happier.
[gasps]
That's right.
The manager takes one look
at her master or mistress
and knows exactly
what they want,
even if it seems ridiculous
on the surface.
I'm sorry, but uh, do you think
you could cast a
little spell for me?
Oh, yeah, the magic thing.
I totally forgot.
Nummy yummy! There, I'm done.
[gasps] So cruel, yet,
I can't get enough!
[JUNICHIRO] This is the
work of a true master.
Sometimes she's a little sassy.
Sometimes she's a little clumsy.
Sometimes she's a little sister.
Yes, even at her age.
Don't question it.
She reaches into her
customer's hearts, and,
if only for a moment,
becomes the character
they most treasure.
[MAKINA gasps]
The way of the maid is not
for the faint of heart.
Well, what do
you think now?
Can you aspire to that
level of greatness,
or have you reached your limit?
[grunts]
Are you kidding?
I haven't even started to fight.
Like I told you before.
I don't quit.
You got it?
[JUNICHIRO]
Uh-huh.
Good luck, then.
[MAKINA]
Moe moe kyun!
My goodness! Back again already?
[BOTH] Hey, hey,
hey, hey, hey, hey!
[MAKINA giggles]
[PATRON H laughs]
[MAKINA]
Farewell, Master! See you soon!
[sighs]
[JUNICHIRO]
So, Twin-Tailed Weirdo,
how does a hard day's work feel?
[gasps]
Time for your test.
Do you know what
maid dignity means?
Let's see.
Having the creativity
and confidence
to think out of the box,
the compassion to understand
what the customer needs,
and the cleverness to adapt
and deliver that to them.
[MAKINA]
Hm.
[JUNICHIRO]
I give you half credit.
Well, it's a start, but I think
you already know the other half.
[gasps]
That's right.
And as I heard you say before,
the philosophy of your
school is to learn, think,
and devise your own answers,
so that your spirit
may experience
true richness and growth.
Isn't that correct?
So what's your point?
Why do you want to expel
Potatoes so badly?
[gasps]
And don't feed me some line a
one episode villain would say,
like "because she's breaking
the rules." I want the truth.
Shut up!
[JUNICHIRO yells]
[thud]
[MAKINA grunts]
[ALL gasp]
Even if you have a lofty
opinion of maid cafes,
that doesn't change the
reality of the situation.
The fact remains
that places like this
are looked down upon by society.
[ALL gasp]
Regardless of anyone's
personal feelings,
I have to protect the
image of our school.
Sorry, but that's final!
Heh.
[gasps]
That's good.
I like where this
story's headed.
We're going to have an
interesting lesson after all.
[gasps]
This is where we'd go
to a commercial break.
We'll bring this battle to its
conclusion in the second act.
[MALE A] Did you catch
that tweet about tonight?
[MALE B]
Yeah, but what does it mean?
[MALE A]
Guess we'll find out at 9:00!
[MALE C] Huh. Might be
worth checking out.
[FEMALE A gasps]
You wanna go?
[FEMALE B]
Why not!
[FEMALE C]
Might be fun!
[MALE A]
Is this the place?
[MALE B]
It's still early.
[FEMALE B]
That tweet was kind of cryptic.
Huh? Second act of what?
C'mon, just run with it.
Here's the scenario.
After working as a maid,
you learn to see their value.
But since society
looks down on them,
in order to protect
your school's image
you've decided to
expel Potatoes, right?
[MAKINA grunts]
Okay, then.
That means all we have to do is
change the way society thinks!
With her!
[ALL gasp]
Huh?
[whimpers]
That has to be a joke, right?
Watch closely.
This is your lesson.
[gasps]
Okay!
Sing your heart out!
[KIRIKO]
Uh...
[JUNICHIRO]
Wow!
That tweet of mine
really got around!
You've got a whole
crowd dying to see you!
Me?
What the heck did you pull?
Now all you have to do is
turn in a perfect performance,
and just like me,
society will be singing the
praises of maids in no time!
'Cause of a handful of people?
Are you insane?
She's right.
I couldn't do something
like that if I wanted to.
Of course you can.
You are a legendary underground
idol singer, aren't you?
Known as the
"maid among maids".
"Razor Girl."
[gasps]
You never showed your face and
you never revealed your name,
but tons of people watched the
dances you posted on NukoVideo.
The mysterious maid
with moves so sharp,
people started calling her
"Razor Girl."
When I saw you at
the school gate,
I felt like I recognized
you from somewhere.
But since I'd never
seen your face,
I didn't want to jump to
conclusions just yet.
Well, anyway, your identity
became crystal clear
after I saw you
working at the café.
[KIRIKO whimpers]
No. I'm sorry! I can't!
[MAKINA]
Hold on a second.
So everything he
said is the truth?
The whole underground
idol singer thing?
[KIRIKO sighs]
Why? I don't get it!
I just.
I've always liked maid costumes.
They're cute.
So, I thought it would be
fun to work at a maid café.
I had to sing and dance a
lot as part of the job.
And then, I really started
to get into performing.
I'd take my uniform
home with me
and come up with new
dances to put online.
I kept it a secret, though.
I'm so dumb.
I... went on and on
about how maids are supposed
to make their masters happy.
But I was only doing
this for myself.
I'm sorry, but Mr. Kagami
was wrong about me.
I'm not a "maid among maids!"
I'm just a big fake!
Nothing but a selfish liar!
[clattering]
[gasps]
Then how do you explain this?
I don't get it.
Pay attention,
Twin-Tailed Weirdo.
This is the other half of your
lesson I was talking about.
What?
[JUNICHIRO]
There's nothing "fake"
about what they're feeling
in these pictures.
You get it now?
You're happy doing
what you love,
and you make a lot other
people happy when you do it.
It's nothing to be ashamed of.
[gasps, giggles]
[JUNICHIRO]
In fact, you should be proud.
[sighs]
[sobs]
All the maids here
really look up to you.
And now, your perfect
stage is waiting.
Give every master
and every mistress
in the world a good show!
Okay!
Please, don't do this.
[KIRIKO gasps]
Give all this up.
I don't want to expel
you from school.
We can work things out.
[gasps]
[MAKINA] But if you
go out there and sing,
there's nothing more I can say.
Don't do something you're
going to regret.
[gasps]
[MAKINA]
I know this is cruel.
But even if you do perform,
it won't change anything.
It's not going to play
out like he said at all!
You'll make a fool of
yourself for nothing!
You can't throw away
a good education
for some delusion a ridiculous
otaku is feeding you!
None of this is important!
It's just a fantasy!
Y'know, maybe you're right.
But getting expelled
won't kill me.
Losing my whole way
of life, on the other hand,
is a fate worse than death.
[MAKINA gasps]
[chuckles]
Pay attention, Twin-Tails.
'Cause this girl is about to
change the whole world!
[CROWD chatters]
[MALE A]
Did they make that tweet
just to watch us wait here?
[MALE C] Come on, you got
nothing better to do, admit it.
[gasps]
Hey! Look!
Whoa!
[MALE A]
I see a girl up there!
[MALE C]
Hey, you're right!
I'm here to serve!
Are you ready?
[CROWD cheers]
[giggles]
[KIRIKO singing in japanese]
[MALE A]
Wow, you see that?
Her moves are crazy sharp!
[MALE C]
Yeah, and look at the screens!
It's on all the
buildings at once.
I don't know how they pulled
that off, but it's super cool!
[MALE B] I've never seen
anything like this!
Record it, quick!
[MALE D] I'm gonna post it,
but what do I name the video?
[MALE B]
Dude, what are you stupid?
There's only one person
with moves like that!
It's Razor Girl,
the "maid among maids!"
[singing continues]
Awesome!
[BODYGUARD]
They're at 10 million views.
Makina. Just so you're aware.
They're streaming this
performance live
and over 10 million people
from around the world
are watching it as we speak.
10 million?
It's quite the
ironic twist, isn't it?
Now if you were to expel her,
it's more likely to hurt
the school's image.
[gasps]
[MAKINA]
I don't understand.
I mean, why did
you take her side
when I just wanted what
was best for the school?
It's not like that.
[gasps]
[laughs] I wasn't siding
with her or against you.
But I will always side with
what is most amusing,
and in this case, Mr.Kagami
was able to bring out
something truly
interesting in her.
In time, perhaps he can make
this entire nation
shine as well.
And I'll be there
aiding his every step.
[MAKINA gasps]
[singing continues]
And that concludes
another lesson!
Thanks, you guys!
[CROWD cheers]
[KIRIKO]
Hi, Kiriko Shikishima here,
AKA Potatoes! I hope
you liked my song!
Also, your order of fries
is coming right up!
In the meantime,
next episode, Mr. Kagami
has to face off against the
baddest dude in the school,
Seijuro Nanami!
Period Five,
"Monster of Icho Academy."
It looks bad for our hero,
but I know just the
person to save the day!
Wait.
She was one of
Mr. Kagami's students, too?