[JUNICHIRO]
I have YD.
You say you've
never heard of it?
What?
I like wearing yukata on
dates? Or yummy dinners?
Wrong!
It's a debilitating illness
where you can only do
what you yearn to do.
I woke up with a revelation.
You need The History of Warfare!
You are now part of
Japan's most popular MMO.
There's a Mega Event
called "Battle of Uro."
I'll be the General,
you'll be my army
and everything that stands
in our way will be dead!
Guys, I'd like to introduce
you all to my partner.
I'm missing a student.
There is still another
truant, remember?
I wasn't the only
student in your class
that had an attendance problem.
You've gotta be kidding me.
Is it really you?
I mean, what are the odds?
The truant Koutaro and Luce
are the same person.
Um... Are you trolling me?
You can't be my teacher.
Okay, wow.
[LUCE] How is it, of all people,
The First found me out?
[JUNICHIRO] This is not how
things were supposed to go!
Damn!
You were supposed to be our last
team member in the battle event!
Where am I supposed
to find another player
on such short notice?!
Uh. Wait, what?
Oh man! I'm really
gonna have to think
--outside of the box this time!
--You're not mad?
I guess I do have
something to say to you
now that I know who you are.
[gasps]
I gotta take care
of this crisis,
so training the team is
your responsibility now!
[gasps]
[SUZUNE]
Luce?
Are you in there?
What happened to you?
[gasps] Oh.
Sorry about that.
I stepped away from my computer.
It's no big deal.
Then why were you freaking out
when she wasn't answering?
[LUCE] So I guess this means...
these kids are my... classmates.
[JUNICHIRO]
C'mon brain.
Everyone's counting on me, I
have to find someone to join us.
Oh... Now that
I think about it,
there's really only
one choice, isn't there?
[SEIJURO bellows]
[SEIJURO]
Stop running!
[yells]
[SEIJURO gasps]
Behold, Fairy Binding.
[SEIJURO grunts]
[SEIJURO] And I thought losing
to Otaku Teacher was bad.
[SUZUNE]
That was amazing, Luce!
Yeah, can you show us
how you did that?
Because I've never
seen anything like it!
[KANAN]
Uh-huh, uh-huh!
I baited the enemy
into charging at me
and then evaded his attacks,
which allowed me to build
my Skill Gauge without
taking any damage.
[KANAN]
Build your what?
The Skill Gauge meter, it
measures the energy you have
to be able to perform
Super Special Attacks.
You can see it in the top
left corner of your screen.
Oh, that thing.
Now I see it.
The bar fills up
as you land hits,
or take them from your opponent.
You'll want to watch it,
so you know when it's full.
'Cause then you can do one of
those Super Special attacks
to get you out of
a pinch or inflict
a whole bunch of damage.
Yeah, now you're getting it!
Man, you are so cool!
Which makes sense;
It takes a special person to put
up with my brother all the time.
What now?
Oh. So The First
has a little sister...
Heh, yeah, I'm sorry if
he's given you any trouble.
He can be really selfish
and an idiot sometimes.
I don't think
that's true at all!
I mean, I can't always tell
what he's thinking, sure,
but he's actually
very open-minded.
I feel comfortable
when I'm with him.
It's like I can really
be myself, y'know?
Wow, I gotta admit,
that's awfully generous of you
to think of Junichiro that way.
[gasps]
What? But it's true.
So what kind of things do you
like to do in your free time?
Other than play video games,
we know that.
Oh, and how'd you
meet my brother anyway?
I'm dying to know.
Long story...
[KISAKI]
Hey!
Uh?
You can't ask people about their
offline lives out of the blue.
That's what we call
"bad 'netiquette."
Uh! Really?! I had no idea!
Really? People game
online for a reason.
Pestering them about their
personal lives is poor manners
when you know nothing
about them IRL.
I am so sorry, Luce!
I didn't know
anything about that!
Please forgive me!
Hey! No worries!
I'm glad she made that mistake
first so I didn't have to.
Luce, I gotta tell you.
That outfit is super cute.
It looks awesome on you, girl!
Oh. Thank you!
It's one of my favorites.
Do you dress like that
in real life?
I'm sure you could pull it off.
What brands do you like?
Yeah! And where do you
like to go shopping?
Are you two kidding me?!
Seriously, what did we
just get done discussing?
[LUCE giggles]
[SEIJURO]
All right, Sister!
[gasps]
We ain't done fighting yet!
[growls]
Okay!
[SUZUNE] Wow. I had a ton more
fun that I thought I would!
Gotta say, I'm pretty impressed.
Huh?
By your talent.
You managed to take a group of
amateurs and turn them
into halfway decent players
in a single day.
That's no small feat.
You should be proud of yourself.
No, you guys are a bunch
of fast learners, that's all!
[SEIJURO]
Hmph.
Even if that were true,
we wouldn't know
what we were doing without
your helpful guidance!
We owe you big time!
We actually stand a chance
in tomorrow's event
and it's all thanks to you!
You didn't have to take time
out of your day to help.
So, thank you...
from all of us.
[CLASS]
Yeah! Thank you, Luce!
I guess your day's wasted.
You prob'ly had no fun hanging
out with "the n00bs."
That's not true!
I had lots of fun!
I promise!
[gasps]
We're looking forward to
kicking butt with you tomorrow.
See you on the battlefield!
[gasps]
I'm looking forward to it, too.
It's gonna be a good time.
There's no way we
can lose after today!
I think so, too!
It's like Luce has
delivered us a blessing
from the Goddess of Victory!
[LUCE]
Huh...?
More like Luce IS
the Goddess of Victory!
So cool!
Would it be all right
if I shake your hand, too?!
[MALE STUDENT B]
Yeah, and me?
[FEMALE STUDENT A]
Don't forget me!
[KANAN] Oh, man.
When did it get so dark?
[KIRIKO] I guess we got
carried away, didn't we?
[SUZUNE]
Hey. There you are.
[JUNICHIRO]
Yo, what's up?
Did you guys put in a
lot of hard work today?
[SUZUNE]
Yeah, but we owe that to Luce
seeing as she took
the time to teach us,
which, by the way, is your job.
Well, you seem rather calm,
so I'm assuming
you found us
another team member?
I got everything taken care of.
There's nothing to worry about.
We're all set
to rock this thing.
I see. I guess that
means you met him, then.
Huh?
Koutaro Araki.
You know, the student who's
missing from your roster?
Didn't you go to meet
with him today?
[JUNICHIRO]
Now that I think about it.
I didn't really talk
to Koutaro, did I?
Wait, you mean you
actually got to see him?
So, what? Is he one of
Seijuro's victims?
Yeah, right.
Look:
He's been gone so long he wasn't
even at opening ceremonies.
There's no way I can beat up a
guy who skips class every day.
You keep track of
everyone you've fought?
That's weird.
[SEIJURO]
You wanna get on the list?!
[JUNICHIRO] Hmm? What's
the matter, Potatoes?
Nothing. I was just thinking,
Koutaro and I were in
the same middle school.
Whoa, seriously?
What was he like back then?
Well... I dunno...
We didn't take the same classes.
Didn't even know he existed
until graduation.
All I ever heard about him was a
rumor that he'd gotten
into some trouble and that's
why no one ever really
saw him after that.
Ah. What kind of trouble?
[KIRIKO] It was something over
spring break in our third year.
I guess he and
a classmate had an incident.
And after that, he stopped
coming to school.
[LUCE sighs]
[LUCE]
What now...?
Everybody ready
to bring the pain?!
[CLASS]
Hell yeah!
All right! Nice game faces!
Save us the speech. Let's show
these guys what we've got!
We're all ready!
There's no way we're gonna lose!
School's in session,
boys and girls!
[JUNICHIRO]
Bam!
Team 2-3 is now registered
and ready for the Battle of Uro!
This is it, class!
[CLASS]
Yeah!
[gasping]
[SEIJURO]
The hell is that?
[MAKINA screams]
[grunts]
[MALE STUDENT A] That's one
way to make an entrance...
[KISAKI]
A dragon?
Who is it?
'Bout time. I was afraid
she wasn't going to make it.
[MAKINA groans]
Ouch...
[SUZUNE]
Holy crap, it's Makina!
I probably should've guessed
you'd be our substitute.
Nice outfit. You pick
that class to show off?
No, I don't even wanna be
a part of this stupid thing!
[growls]
Okay, Mr. Kagami!
You told me if I helped you
win this stupid game,
I'd get a chance
to talk to the truant.
So is he here,
or were you lying?
I wouldn't dream of it!
In fact, him coming back
to class may hinge
on your involvement,
so you'd better try hard.
No slacking!
I swear, if you're
doing this to get a laugh...
...you're dead meat!
This outfit is super vulgar!
Mr. Kagami?
You should see this.
[SUZUNE] How are we
already in the finals?
That can't be right.
[KISAKI] It can be if
only two teams register
to compete in the event.
[KIRIKO] Then we only
need to win one fight!
[KANAN]
Wow, we're pretty lucky, huh?
[JUNICHIRO]
No, we're not.
[GROUP]
Huh?
It looks like
the other teams ran off
when they saw that
Monsters Factory had entered
the tournament.
Are they that strong of
players or something?
Oh, you bet they are.
They've been playing Uroboros
since it was in beta testing.
Not only that, their guild
has won every single
multiplayer event for years.
They chose their team name
because they all use
monster-type characters.
[GIRLS whimper]
[SUZUNE]
And we're expected to beat them?
Absolutely. If anyone can stop
their win streak, it's us.
Hey! About time you signed on!
We're counting on you.
Don't let me down, okay?
[gasps]
Luce, what's wrong? C'mon! Luce!
[LUCE]
"Mr. Kagami.
I'm sorry, but I can't be
around the others.
It's best for everyone
if I keep my distance.
You should still be able to
compete in the event
even if I'm away
from my computer.
Koutaro Araki."
Hey, is everything okay?
Not really.
Luce signed on, but is away
from the computer in real life
to avoid having to play.
What? But why would she do that?
I'm going to figure that out,
but I'll need time.
You guys are gonna have to guard
our characters until I get back.
Hold out as long as you can
and we'll take care of the rest
once we return.
We'll have to fight
those guys without you?
[SEIJURO]
That's gonna be a problem.
You think so?
For him?
Yeah, 'cause I'm gonna finish
these bastards off
before he even
gets a shot at 'em.
You'd better hurry. She schooled
me pretty bad in training.
I'd hate for her not to
see all her hard work
pay off in the end.
Plus, I'd like to return the
favor to her once this is done.
We wanna win this thing for Luce
to show her how great she is!
So we'll buy you as
much time as we can afford!
Thanks, you guys.
[MAKINA]
Well, what are you waiting for?
You need to go.
This Luce person is your
missing student, right?
If that's the case,
I'll do everything I can
to cover for you
while you're gone!
Well, all right then!
I'll be back!
Okay, it's time
to start the lesson!
[STUDENTS whimper]
[JUNICHIRO panting]
Huh? I found you!
Hold up, Luce!
[gasps]
[JUNICHIRO] What do you
think you're doing?!
Wait! C'mon!
Go away! I beg you!
You don't need me!
You can beat them yourself!
I'd just slow you down!
I wish you'd slow down!
Argh!
[JUNICHIRO]
Stop running!
[MONSTERS growling, snarling]
'Kay, guys.
We have to buy enough time
for my brother to get back
to the game with Luce.
Fight wisely and
focus on healing.
Until the two of them
return to the battle.
I'll stand in as
acting party leader.
[STUDENTS murmur]
[SUZUNE] Defending their
characters is our top priority.
Here we go.
[MONSTERS snarling]
[STUDENTS growling]
[STUDENTS screaming, yelling]
Now... Nowhere left
for you to run.
You're right.
And this is as good a place
as any for us to stop,
since it's where we first met.
[JUNICHIRO]
I don't think I follow.
I've been like this for
as long as I can remember.
I'm sure it was a real
inconvenience for my mom.
[LUCE'S MOTHER]
Come on, we have to go.
Boys clothes are
over here, sweetie.
Are you listening to me?
Look at how cute it is.
[LUCE'S MOTHER]
Oh, Koutaro...
[FEMALE CLERK]
Thank you for coming in!
[LUCE'S MOTHER]
Well, I guess if you're happy.
[LUCE]
I couldn't help it.
I loved cute things.
I wanted to be cute.
I kept it a secret
from everyone else,
but as I grew older, I started
wearing my cute clothes
around the house all the time.
But during spring break
back in middle school...
[LUCE]
I shouldn't have to be afraid.
I wanna go outside
like this, too.
[LUCE] I wanna know if other
people think I look cute.
It should be okay as long as I
don't see anyone I know, right?
[KOUSUKE]
Hey, Araki!
[LUCE gasps]
[SATOSHI] What the hell, dude,
why are you dressed like that?
Well, I... The thing is...
Ha! I know!
You had to lose
a bet or something!
How about you whisper sweet
nothings in my ear, Missy?
[LUCE whimpers]
No!
[KOUSUKE gasps, yells]
[LUCE whimpers]
[body thuds]
[sirens wailing]
I'm sorry...
You think that makes us even?!
Look what you did to me, idiot!
I don't care if you're sorry!
So lame.
Why are you such
a little freak?!
[gasps]
[LUCE]
I'm so sorry...
[KOUSUKE] Why are you
such a little freak?!
[cell phone beeps]
[LUCE]
Ah.
[LUCE] A local player
tag from Uroboros?
Someone's in my room.
[door clacks, creaks]
[JUNICHIRO] Oh wow,
this place is awesome!
You've got a lot of
rare items in here!
And your setup is
top tier! Looks great!
Luce, huh?
I'm surprised we haven't met,
I know almost everyone who's
as highly ranked as you.
Guess you don't do
multiplayer stuff much.
Kind of a waste!
[LUCE] Great, this guy's
judging me, too...
[JUNICHIRO] Well,
it's time for us to go!
[gasps]
Huh...?
Let's team up!
We'll face this world together.
You can call me
"The First," partner.
Hold on.
Why should I go with you?
[JUNICHIRO] Because it's
dangerous to go alone.
Besides, if we team up, you can
get even more cute items.
Everyone in the
whole game, if you like.
[LUCE]
After you found me that day,
my Luce persona became the
most important part of my life.
Because I could go out
and be seen, thanks to you.
But I know if I keep
talking with my classmates,
someone's going
to learn the truth.
Just like last time...
[KOUSUKE] Why are you
such a little freak?!
I just can't go through
something like that!
Not again!
[whimpers]
Check this out.
Your classmates are fighting
desperately right now
waiting for you to join them.
[gasps]
--[MONSTERS growling]
--[STUDENTS grunting]
[JUNICHIRO]
They all believe that,
if they can hold out
long enough,
you'll be back to save the day.
I think where you should be
right now is with them.
That's the reason I came all
the way out here to get you.
I know you'll get scared
and you'll want to
run away from them.
That's fine.
'Cause I'll chase you to
bring you back every time.
I don't get it.
What's the point?
C'mon, you know...
My reason's obvious.
[JUNICHIRO] Whether it's
in a game or real life,
it doesn't matter to me,
because you're my partner.
[gasps]
[chuckles]
--[MONSTER HAMMERHEAD growls]
--[SUZUNE] Let me go!
[gasps]
[MONSTER HAMMERHEAD chuckles]
[whimpers]
--[MONSTER HAMMERHEAD screams]
--[SUZUNE yelps]
Whoa. Is that...?
[LUCE]
Sorry I'm so late, everyone!
[gasps]
--[MAKINA gasps]
--[KISAKI chuckles]
[STUDENTS gasping]
[SEIJURO]
Hmph.
I can't thank you all enough!
You've done very well!
Now leave the rest to us!
[CROWD gasping]
Front lines pull back, now!
Lure the enemy in close like
you learned in your training!
[STUDENTS growling]
[MONSTERS snarling]
There you go!
They got impatient and took the
bait, hook, line, and sinker
right into our territory.
Back lines, you're up!
Use your most powerful spells.
Let 'em have it!
[STUDENTS yelling]
[MONSTERS roaring]
Hey, WTF?
These guys were DOA,
why are they suddenly l33t?
Oh, crap, we're screwed!
JK?
[MONSTER RABBIT]
No! We definitely picked
the wrong fight this time!
[gasps]
FML...
That's Godspeed
Red Knight, The First!
And his partner,
the Ironclad Nun Luce!
Spiritual Binding!
[PURPLE MONSTER]
No! They got us!
[JUNICHIRO grunts]
Skill gauge, charge complete.
Dual Wield Flurry
Skill Activate!
Bullet Sword Infinity!
[MONSTERS yelling]
[ANNOUNCER]
Winner: Team 2-3.
[cheering]
[JUNICHIRO]
All right!
And that's the end
of today's lesson!
[cheering, luaghing]
Amazing! We really
won, everybody!
I can't believe we did it!
It's all thanks to you, Luce!
No way! I couldn't have
done it without you all.
[JUNICHIRO]
Hmph.
I don't think I've ever felt
this happy after winning a game!
I know! This makes me
wanna keep on playing it!
Me, too! I wonder what our
next quest is gonna be!
[gasps]
Whatever it is, you'll
play with us again, right?
Uh, sure.
[LUCE] I agreed out of reflex,
but I really have to stop.
I can't get too close.
If I keep playing with them,
they'll figure out
the truth about me...
That I'm a boy...
That I'm their classmate...
Everything...
[LUCE]
What now?
What should I do...?
[KISAKI]
This is Kisaki Tenjoin,
also known as
the Black Mage Kisaki.
That comeback we made
really got my blood boiling.
That's the stuff of legends!
In the next episode,
Seijuro saves Luce
from some skirt chasers.
As a result, Luce reveals
to him his true identity
as the missing student
Koutaro Araki.
Period eleven,
"The Outside World."
I'm not sure what Junichiro
has up his sleeve,
but my interest has been piqued.
Specifically in Koutaro Araki.