[man roaring]
[growling]
[both panting]
[continues growling]
[wind howls]
[soft thunder]
Hadouken!
Ohh!
Yaahh!
[panting]
Arrhh! Ooh!
Blahh!
[grunts softly]
Gouki.
[battle roar]
[battle grunts]
Die, Gouki!
[grunting]
I will not die!
[speaking Japanese]
[roars]
[thunder]
[Girl]
Gouki.
Gouki!
Uhh...
Are you all right?
Uh...
Mmhh.
[Man]
Are you
really in pain?
I think
I overdid it a bit.
This was supposed to be
a non-contact sparring.
But I had no
choice because you used
the forbidden skill.
Remember. The Old Master
has forbidden the Dark Hadou.
Uhh!
Hey, watch it!
This could get
infected really bad.
Huh. Infected?
Don’t move.
There.
Hmmhh.
[crow caws distantly]
[gong]
[Man, angrily]
It is forbidden!
But, Master,
I just don’t
understand why.
How many times do I
have to tell you
you cannot use
the Dark Hadou!
I still
don’t understand.
It’s senseless.
To mindlessly follow
this path that’s laid out
as if our predecessors’
teaching is absolute?
I don’t agree.
No matter the sacrifice
or bloodshed,
it’s courage,
courage to tread
a thorny trail
should be the goal
of every martial
arts master.
Is that all
you have to say?
What you are describing...
[grunts]
...that is
not courage.
Oh, no.
It’s only arrogance.
Master.
Master!
Sayaka.
It may be
hard to believe,
I know,
but father wants
what’s best for you.
I know that.
But...
...I have my own path
to follow.
I really wanted Master
to understand.
[sighs]
[thud]
[gasps]
Mmhh!
What’s the matter?
Are you all right?
Damn. Not again.
Again? What is it?
Are you feeling
sick or something?
It’s nothing.
[breathes painfully]
Just stay away.
From his appearance,
he must
have secretly been
using the Dark Hadou.
I am sorry.
Don’t be a fool.
It is nothing
that you need
to apologize for.
Right.
To be quite honest
with you,
I had been truly hoping
that this day would
never come to pass.
But now it has arrived.
The bad karma
which is flowing
in our bodies,
it is bad karma,
indeed.
Yes, Master.
We cannot leave him
alone any longer.
It’s unthinkable.
Understood.
We have absolutely
no other choice now.
But if I fail
at this task,
the consequences
will be unacceptable.
Gouken, you
are going to end
this cycle of bad karma.
[growling]
Now, Gouken.
Gouki. Uhh.
I am choosing
my path.
Your path
is not the way.
Forgive me.
[roaring]
[gasps]
[breathes shakily]
Gouken.
Huh?
What is it,
Sayaka?
They’re gone,
both of them!
Gone?
Father’s gone.
And Gouki, too!
[low growl]
[growls]
Seeing you like this is
a great disappointment.
It’s deplorable.
[roars]
Forgive me, Gouki.
[panting]
Uhh! Uhh!
Sayaka.
I’m all right.
Please go ahead
without me.
Hurry!
[whimpers]
Sayaka. You can’t be.
[grunting]
[whimpers]
Huh?
Oh!
Ohh! Oh! Master!
Master!
[panting]
Ohh! Gouki,
why in the world
would you do
something like this?
What is the matter
with you?
Gouki!
This?
Are you telling me
this is the path
you choose?
Answer me!
Gouki!
Are you just going
to throw away
everything you have
and leave? Huh?
You don’t know
what you’re doing!
You’re completely insane!
Your happiness
was right there,
within your reach!
But this?
Don’t you understand?
Gouki!
[bird chirps]
[birds chirping]
Oh.
Uh...
Is there...
someone here
that you knew?
Uh, my Master
is here.
Uh, his dojo
was right up
there.
Is that so?
Uh...well,
what about you?
My father and mother
are here.
I live close by,
so I come here
every day
to water the plants.
Would you like
to borrow my bucket?
I can come back later
and pick it up.
No, thank you.
I have to
deliver this.
I see.
Then...I must
be going now.
[crow caws distantly]
This place has not
changed one bit.
It’s just like
it was back then.
[eerie wind blows]
Huh? What?
[loud splintering]
Hey. What the hell
is going on?
[gasps]
I can’t...believe...
my eyes.
You. You killed
old Master Gouken!
Damn you!
[snorts]
What’s this about?
Tryin’
to challenge me, huh?
Let’s go! Just say when!
[no audible dialogue]
Huh? Wait!
[birds screech,
wings flapping]
Mmhh. Wha...
I guess I was dreaming.
[clinking]
Mmm-- Huh? Uhh?
[sizzling]
Huh?
[man cackling]
What?
Heh heh heh!
You did a pretty
good job
of sensing me,
but you still have
a long way to go.
I’d say some more training
would do you a lot of good.
Training?
Who are you?
Me? I’m
just an old monk.
So. Do you intend
on fighting that man?
Huh?
To thank you
for the lunch,
how about I give you
a little bit of instruction?
Yee-aah!
Huh?
Aah! Yeah.
Yeah.
Huh. Not bad...
for an old guy.
Street fight
is your preference?
Here you go!
Ooh!
[grunting]
What’s the matter, kid?
You’re not even fighting back.
Or perhaps you’re
just not capable.
[chuckles]
All right!
That’s it!
I don’t waste time
fighting old men like you!
Come on! You’re
nothing but talk,
young fella!
T-hutt!
Damn it! Uhh!
Okay, now
I’m mad, grandpa!
Hyah!
A-ha! Getting
a little motivated,
are you?
[shouting in Japanese]
Huh? He knows
the same style as me!
[chuckles]
Pretty good lunge.
Huhh!
Here I am.
[roars]
[grunting]
[groaning]
That’s it! You're
finished, grandpa.
You might
as well give up.
This is the end.
I got you
in this hold.
You’re paralyzed.
Are you quite sure
I’m paralyzed?
What?
Hutt!
[groans]
Uhh!
Heh heh heh heh--
Mmm?
I’ve been easy on you
because of your advanced
age,
but now...
Oh, using
the Dark Hadou.
Bad idea to rely
strictly on that.
How immature.
Prepare yourself,
grandpa!
Hadouken!
Whoop!
Here you go.
Huh?
Ohh...
Nothin’ to it.
[chuckles]
Here. I’ll send it
back.
[gasps] Ohh!
[groans painfully]
[moans]
[coughs]
Ooh!
Uhh!
Here.
Uhh-- Huh?
Well, junior, have
you had enough?
Yeah.
I give up, grandpa.
You sure did
beat me, all right.
Even my Hadouken was
ineffective against you.
Are you shocked
to have been defeated
by an old thief
like me
with all
my experience?
Hey, I like you.
Come on
over to my place.
Huh?
Well, what’s the matter?
Aren’t you going
to eat anything?
You must be hungry.
Grandpa.
We had a tough fight
just minutes ago,
and now we’re sitting
here in your dining room
having a meal peacefully.
So, why did you
bring me here,
grandpa?
Come on. Now, aren’t
you going to eat?
Nnngg...Of course
I’m going to.
But I just keep wondering
about who you are, grandpa.
I mean, what is
your story for real?
I’m just a monk.
Plain and simple,
Ryu.
Hmm.
This is
my granddaughter
Fuka.
[gasps]
Oh, it’s you!
Oh, hello.
What? Do you two
know each other?
Yep. Sort of.
Um, Grandfather,
is this the apprentice
you told me about?
Wha?
That’s right.
Today is his first day.
Now, be sure
to treat him well.
Wait! I haven’t
said one word
about an apprenticeship
with you or anybody else.
What’s your hesitation?
Come on. I’d like
to propose a toast.
Me? I can’t drink.
Nonsense. Drink up.
[chuckles] Well,
enjoy yourselves.
Uh, yeah. Thanks.
What do you think?
Isn’t she a nice girl?
Uh, oh, yeah.
Do you like her?
Uh, sure.
Well, then,
that’s it!
You want to marry
Fuka, don’t you?
[coughs]
Ouch.
What are you
talking about?
I’m old now.
I’m anxious to see
my granddaughter
in her hour of glory.
Great-grandchildren,
too.
You’re kidding me.
Really,
Grandfather!
Enough is enough!
Give the poor guy
a break.
Look. Now she’s upset.
By the way...
what are you
training for
specifically?
Uh, well...I don’t
really wanna...
Tell me, Ryu.
I, um...
Still undecided, eh? Huh?
You’re searching
for something.
The path to a so-called
true martial arts master.
How could you
know that?
If you like,
you can stay here
till you find
what you’re looking for.
I’ll take
good care of you.
Grandpa, why are you
so concerned about me?
[chuckles]
By the way, Ryu,
the man
that you encountered
earlier today--
that man
was a true demon,
wasn’t he?
Gouki.
I remember seeing him
when I was still a kid,
when I was just starting
to understand about the world.
I don’t remember
where or when
I first saw him.
I was fascinated...
but scared more
than anything else.
[soft growl]
Those huge hands
that he had.
Come to think of it,
it must be my fate
to fight that man.
That must be it.
Interesting how
things work out.
I ended up staying
at this old man’s house
for a while.
Life there was fun.
But I couldn’t find
answers about myself
or about my impending
battle with that monster.
And yet,
time seemed to fly.
[grunting]
[grunting continues]
Ohh...Ohhh!
Uhh...
[Grandpa
chuckles]
[groaning]
[stretching
sound]
[groans]
Good morning
to you.
How can I be out here
shopping like this
instead of
preparing myself?
That man
killed a master.
He actually killed him
with one blow.
I know the Master
has forbidden me
to fight that man
under any circumstances.
But what is it
that I really want to do?
Sorry about this.
Huh? Oh.
You’re busy
with your training,
and here I made you
come shopping with me.
Oh. Uh...no.
Not a problem.
Um...what about
mackerel today?
That sounds good.
[crow caws distantly]
[gong]
Shopping took a little longer
than expected, didn’t it?
Yeah.
So, have you
been practicing
martial arts
since you
were little?
Yes. But I really
started getting serious
when I began training
under Master Gouken.
And what about
your parents?
They died
when I was little.
I’m sorry
I brought it up.
No. You don’t
need to worry.
To be honest,
I don’t remember
anything.
[gong]
I know
that I was left
to be raised
at a temple
when I was just a baby,
and I have nothing more
than vague memories
of that time.
Eventually,
I left that temple.
And...
did you run away?
Run away? Yeah.
I couldn’t bear
the loneliness.
I was out of control
and did reckless things
back then.
Then I started training
under Master Gouken.
Life was more structured
and more serene.
Until that day...
when that man
appeared again.
It was raining that day.
Do you remember
the rain, Gouken?
You’ll pay!
No, Ryu.
[strained breathing]
[rapid, short breaths]
[Ryu]
But...
[struggles to breathe]
But....
Ryu.
What is it?
What, Fuka?
Ryu, why do you feel
that you have to
fight such a man?
[snickers]
You know,
my father was
a martial arts
master, too.
Yeah?
Yes, just like you.
My father
wanted to become
a true
martial arts master.
And he trained
under my grandfather.
One day there was
a big match.
My father died
in that battle.
[sniffles]
Don’t mind me.
I’m sorry.
It’s all right.
[woman screams]
Huh?
You’re Ryu!
Oh, my!
You...are...
I found you!
At last!
Ohh...
[muttering]
Mmm...mmm...
What
an appetite!
Uhh. Mmm.
[gulps]
Now I’m fine.
I could hardly
believe it when
you passed out.
That’s because it took
a while to get here,
and I hardly
ate or drank
the whole time.
Where was it
that you traveled from?
I started
in Tokyo.
Tokyo?
I really wanted
to find you, Ryu.
Yeah?
Wanted to find Ryu?
Hmm. Me?
You must be
exhausted.
No, no.
Wait a minute.
What I would like
to know is,
who was it who told you
to look for me here?
Ken told me.
Ken did?
Are you telling me
that you know Ken?
Yes. I met him
in Tokyo.
Ken told me that
he was coming here
for the anniversary
of the Master’s death.
Um...
Ryu?
Yeah?
Please.
I want you to fight
a match with me!
What?
What in the world
are you talking about?
Ever since I saw you,
I knew you weren’t just
a regular street fighter.
I knew you were
a true fighter,
and I’ve been
training extra hard
for this opportunity.
That’s what
I’m talkin' about.
[Grandpa]
Ha ha ha! She’s expecting
great things of you, Ryu.
What is a true
fighter, anyway?
I am not a true fighter.
I haven’t come close
to that level yet.
I have to fight...
or I’m afraid
I’ll never be content.
All right,
let’s do it.
Huh?
It’ll be
a learning
experience.
[excited breath]
All right!
[laughs excitedly]
Let’s go!
I’m ready for you!
[panting]
Uh...
[shouting in Japanese]
Huhh!
Yahh!
[grunting,
breathing hard]
Ryu, you’re
holding back on me.
Huh?
You’re not using
all of your ability.
But why?
’Cause you think I'm weak?
That’s an insult!
Uhhh!
Huhh!
Uhh! Uhh!
[sobs]
Sakura!
[shakily]
I’m all right.
Ryu. Again.
Please.
[Ryu]
This girl.
She stands up to me
with all her strength,
knowing she’s
no match for me.
[Sakura coughs,
gasps]
[Sakura grunting]
[fight grunts]
She’s right.
There’s no question.
I really do
want to fight.
I’m going to fight
that man!
[Sakura shouts, groans]
[grunts, sighs]
[sighs, breathes slowly]
Mmhh...
[grunts painfully]
Thank you very much.
It was a very good
lesson for me.
No. I thank you.
I’m the one
who learned here.
Hmm?
It’s obvious.
No matter
the consequences,
I just want
to fight that man.
I have to fight.
Or I can never find
what I’m looking for.
[steam hissing,
water splashing]
[sighs]
That’s great.
[sighing]
[both laugh]
[splat]
I see. Then you’re
not his real granddaughter,
Fuka?
Well, no. I know
that we’re distant
relatives, though.
So you’ve had
a tough life.
Not really.
I mean...
some people think so,
but at least
I had my grandpa around.
Grandpa is such
a funny man,
isn’t he?
But he seems so old.
I wonder how old he is.
Well, he’s been
the same ever since
I can remember.
I guess he must be
over 90.
Wow! That’s amazing!
Yeah, and he is healthy,
and he really
is young at heart.
Hey!
Wahh!
Oh, Grandfather!
He really is
funny, huh?
Oh.
Fuka, you know,
I think Ryu
actually enjoys it.
What?
To fight.
I wonder if he is
going to fight.
[sighs]
It’s morning.
Those clouds
look pretty bad.
Probably a storm
comin’ in.
Are you leaving,
Ryu?
Grandpa.
[chuckles]
Apparently, you are.
You are leaving.
You’ve made up your mind.
Go to the old
castle ruins
behind Gotuku Temple.
He will most certainly
appear there.
Accept your fate, Ryu.
[rain falling]
[yawning]
Good morning,
Fuka.
Oh. It’s raining.
Have you seen
Ryu yet?
He left early...
before dawn.
Huh?
[panting]
Go back, Ken Masters.
Who the hell
are you, old man?
You cannot get involved
in this battle.
This is the fate
of those two.
Maybe so.
But what does this
have to do with you,
huh?
Sorry. I have to reach
Ryu,
and anybody who gets in my way
is gonna regret it.
You got that?
[blow delivered]
Uhhhh!
Hmm. Not as good
as you claim.
Let go!
Grandpa, I can’t
let him go through
with this.
Ryu is fine.
He doesn’t need
a guardian anymore.
Uhh!
What are you saying?
You know, I followed Ryu
all the way out here to--
You are a pupil
of Gouken, right?
So?
I know why you’re here.
Huh?
To prevent
Ryu’s Dark Hadou
from being awakened
by those two
when they fight
each other,
and to prevent
another tragedy
from happening.
Gouken had a kind
heart and soul.
You. Who the hell are you?
[rumbling]
[steam hissing]
Master.
[roars softly]
[growls]
[grunting]
[Ken]
How can you say that
Ryu’s Dark Hadou
won’t awaken?
Do you have any idea
what the Dark Hadou
really is, old man?
Yes. The Dark Hadou
has the power to destroy
every living thing
in this world.
Long ago,
there lived a people
with a natural ability
to fight with titanic force.
Hadouken!
Hadou--
Aaahhh!
[grunts]
[growls]
[Grandpa]
Many of these people
were used by those
who ruled at the time.
Their sole purpose
was to fight.
[growling]
Aah!
But they did not deserve
to be used for such evil.
Now, one day,
a horrible event
took place.
Huhh!
The days
of consecutive killing
began to awaken
the devil
that lay dormant
within them.
Once the devil
is awakened,
it is said to consume
not only the person’s body
but that person’s
entire being!
Ken, that is
the true identity
of the Dark Hadou.
And those two
have inherited
the contaminated
bloodline!
[chuckles softly]
Unfortunately,
the cycle of bad karma
has not been broken.
Huh?
What power!
My skills...
don’t work at all
against him.
Gouken!
I was not wrong
to walk the path
of a fighter.
The fact that Ryu is here
proves I’m right!
[grunting]
[gasps]
Aah!
Fuka. What is this?
Uh...huh?
Ryu.
[growling]
He’s so strong!
My blocking arm
is starting to feel numb.
But I know I can win if I--
The hell with being
a true fighter!
What on earth
is the difference,
anyway?
Damn!
Damn!!
Uhh!
Aaahh! Aah!
[roaring]
Yes! That’s right, Ryu.
That is
the power coursing
within our blood.
The wakeup call
of a true fighter!
[growls]
Oh, what is this?
[gasps]
The detestable events
of the past
all relate to the blood
flowing through the veins
of those people.
This evil blood
ultimately causes men
to destroy
not only their enemies,
but also their allies,
their loved ones,
and themselves.
Hoohh!
[growling] Hoohh!
Come on, Ryu.
All you want
is to be strong.
That is
our miserable fate.
What’s this?
Uhh.
Fuka.
But, uh...
Ryu, your path to become
a true fighter
has been obscured.
Through your reverence
for your teacher,
you’ve forsaken
your natural thirst
to be strong.
You’re wrong.
It’s made me strong.
[growling]
Die, you!
Uhh!
[growling]
Uhh...
The one...
who became...
...strong.
Uhh.
[splat]
Uhh...
So...
this is the end...
Gouken.
The end of the one
who was swallowed up.
[thud]
My name is Gouki!
The one who became strong...
someday...someday,
I intend to fight you again.
[Grandpa]
It was a long time ago.
A man left a newborn child
in my care.
He said the mother had died.
He said she died
shortly after giving birth
to the baby boy.
Before he left,
the man made me promise
not to let the child
follow in the father’s
path. That child
was away from me
for a brief moment.
But...
[grunts]
Go now.
I kept the promise
that I made to you
that day...
Gouken.
I’m tired.
I wonder why it feels
as if I’ve lived too long.
[wind roars]
[birds twittering peacefully]
[deep rumbling]
Closed-Captioned By
J.R. Media Services, Inc.
Burbank, CA