What?!
[OKAZAKI, OURA yell]
[TSUTOMU grunts]
[BOTH whimper]
[SUZUKI] Is this some kind
of prank or something?
[TANAKA]
Has to be.
That's the only explanation.
[SOLDIER 21A]
Stay together.
[SOLDIER 21B]
Move, and we shoot.
Please, Hayato!
[OURA]
Do something!
[KENTO]
Remain calm.
Do as we tell you,
and no one gets hurt.
[SAKURAKO]
Kento?
[SHOKO]
What the...?
I'm sorry,
but I have my orders.
[IWAGAMI] It is the official
stance of this government
that DEAVA represents
a clear and present threat.
They are the enemy.
Whereas in Nesta,
Japan has a staunch friend.
DEAVA will be dismantled.
[SUBETE] The Book of Verbalism
exerts irresistible power
over everyone and
everything in its vicinity.
If after uncovering it he'd
gone straight to this country's
heads of state,
my father would have
turned the tide in
his favor from the outset.
Alas, he didn't. The fool.
[NESTA]
Come now, Subete.
He refrained
that you might grow.
It's perfect.
The battles,
the agony of defeat...
They were necessary.
They are what
brought me to myself!
I will beat Akira.
If his one true desire is
to save the world, well...
I shall be the one to end it.
The joy of laughter!
Smiles! Harbingers of happiness.
I crush the very concept!
[SUBETE]
Verbalize and rejoice.
For today I set you free.
An M.J.B.K.
that destroys laughter?
Only a first step,
rest assured.
Destroying the very
culture of written language?
That requires Aquarion Logos.
Dear Maia...
Merge with me
and cleanse this world.
[MAIA gasps]
[KENTO] Be smart.
Don't try to resist.
If you think I'm joking,
look at my eyes.
I'm as serious
as a heart attack.
He's right, y'know.
The eyes say everything.
[SAKURAKO gasps]
So that's what's going on.
Thought so.
Yeah, fine.
We're cooperating. See?
[SOLDIER 21A]
Freeze!
[SOLDIER 21B]
Hey!
[SAKURAKO]
It's all right.
I need you to activate
Vector Two remotely.
Trust me.
Be discreet as possible.
[SHOKO gasps]
[SAKURAKO]
Please.
Why would you
need Aquarion Logos?
Because...
The coming of
Aquarion Logos represents
the end of the world
as we know it!
You're gonna end the world
because of your
grudge against Akira?
This is insane!
How can you be so selfish?!
[slap]
[groans]
I won't be condescended
to by a puppet!
No... Subete, don't.
[SUBETE]
I will outshine Akira!
There's no time to waste.
[MAIA] Because he's on
the verge of disappearing.
[SUBETE]
Merge with me, Maia.
[MAIA]
Never!
I refuse to merge
with someone like you!
And I won't stand by
while Akira vanishes!
[SOLDIER 21C]
What?!
[SOLDIER 21A]
Huh?!
[KENTO yells]
[SAKURAKO growls]
[SOLDIERS yelling, groaning]
[ALL yelling]
Dude, what the hell
just happened up in here?
[SHOKO]
I don't know!
The manager asked me to
launch Vector Two on autopilot,
so I did. That's all, I swear!
That was a stupid move!
Akira, go!
Right! Yes ma'am!
[HAYATO]
Kaibuki!
[SAKURAKO] Vectors and pilots
are bound by Verbalism--
They're drawn to each other.
By sending Vector Two
out on autopilot,
it should seek out Maia for us!
[SUBETE]
What is Vector Two doing here?!
[SUBETE yells]
[SUBETE groaning]
Maia, you...
Fire!
[SHOKO squeals]
Get away from me!
You bastard! That's my
woman you're messin' with!
[gunshot]
Crap...
Tsutomu!
[TSUTOMU]
What are you doing?
Get out of his line of fire!
[SHOKO]
Not happening!
[TSUTOMU yells]
[SHOKO]
Oh, god! Oh, god!
No! Hang in there, sweetie!
Don't you even
think about dying!
[TSUTOMU]
What?
With your boobs touching me?
Not a chance.
Idiot!
Damn...
We've done what we could.
It's up to Akira now.
We gave him an opening,
launching Vector Two.
Our role in this has played out.
Akira...
[SAKURAKO] Now, if only
Vector Ga would activate
and start devouring concepts...
[AKIRA]
Verbalize.
[SOLDIER 21F] Someone
tell me where I am, please?
[SAKURAKO]
Sick bay, stat!
[KENTO]
Get a stretcher over here!
[HAYATO]
Hurry! He's bleeding out!
One look at your eyes
was enough to tell me
you and these men were in thrall
to the Book of Verbalism.
Damn.
We have to find a way
to neutralize its power,
or we'll never get through this.
[KENTO]
The monument's our only option.
Vector Ga can't be
activated by computer.
We'll just have to cross our
fingers and have faith in Akira.
[SAKURAKO]
I don't like this gamble,
but your little stunt
has left us no choice.
[KENTO]
I'm sorry.
I'd have tried to warn you,
but they had me
under surveillance.
[beeping noise]
[AKIRA] I'm going on ahead.
I've got this.
[HAYATO]
What?! Don't be a jackass!
You're alone!
Well, c'mon! Let's help!
We can't.
It's f-fine.
Shoko and I will
stay with Tsutomu.
Stay strong.
Of c-course.
[MAIA]
He came here for me.
[SUBETE gasps]
[NESTA]
Is something wrong?
[SUBETE]
No. Not at all.
I'll launch.
[NESTA humming]
[giggles]
My, what a splendid party!
Perhaps I should join;
have some fun.
Come now. Shall we dance?
[maniacal laughter]
[HAYATO] Are you ever not
going to be a pain in the ass?
[KARAN] We really don't
mind helping, you know.
[MAIA]
Akira!
[AKIRA]
You're late.
I'm sorry.
Okay! All units merge!
[KARAN, MAIA]
Roger!
[AKIRA]
Genesis Merge.
[MAIA]
Shout it!
[KARAN, HAYATO]
Fly!
[AKIRA, MAIA]
Aquarion!
[KARAN, HAYATO]
[AKIRA, MAIA]
San!
[ROBO GRYPHON 11A screeches]
[HAYATO, KARAN]
Gai!
[AKIRA]
Where is it?
[MAIA]
Subete...
[SUBETE] Vector Ga, the machine
that ended the legend.
All that power--show it to me!
[MALE STAFF MEMBER 21A]
He's not stabilizing!
[MALE DOCTOR 21A]
Lidocaine. Hundred mil.
[MALE STAFF MEMBER 21B]
Where's that donor packet?
We need a transfusion, stat!
[FEMALE STAFF MEMBER 21A]
Patient's vitals are dropping.
[MALE DOCTOR 21A]
Damn it, we're going in.
Prep for surgery.
Tsutomu...
[SAKURAKO]
Kikogami's with him.
Yeah.
Now what?!
[FEMALE OPERATOR 1A] We've got
confirmation of several
unidentified humanoid giants
appearing in Shinjuku!
[SAKURAKO]
You're kidding me...
This isn't possible.
Aquarions?
[NESTA]
My angels of slaughter.
Come now. Let's dance.
[CROWD gasping]
[CROWD screaming]
[screaming continues]
[laughing]
[laughing continues]
Oh no!
She's gone on the offensive!
[laughing]
Vile chicken scratch!
I curse your existence!
You are a blight!
[CROWD screaming]
I have to save them.
I can't let her
do any more damage.
[MAIA gasps]
[AKIRA]
What?
[NESTA]
Very soon.
What's the matter?
Talk to me!
[NESTA]
He will...
[MAIA whimpering]
[AKIRA]
That look on your face...
[garbled voice]
Are you okay? Maia!
[NESTA]
...disappear.
[MAIA]
No...
No!
[VECTOR GA] Nesta, I shall
devour the very concept of you.
If you want Maia,
you have to go through me!
Akira...
[VECTOR GA]
Devour...
Devour! Devour!
Wait! Don't you
know what's happening?!
Don't you know
what you're doing?!
If you go through with this,
you'll disappear forever!
[AKIRA]
Yeah, so?
[MAIA]
You idiot!
[M.J.B.K. laughing]
Get out of our way!
Damn.
We have to think of something
before it's too late!
[M.J.B.K. laughing]
[NESTA humming]
Serves you right.
[CROWD screaming]
Please, no...
What can I do?
[NESTA] You were able
to manifest a power
you never could have
found on your own.
You've tapped into
the wellspring of my power.
[MAIA gasps]
Akira... Forgive me.
[AKIRA gasps]
[AKIRA]
No!
What are you doing?! Stop!
Maia! Come back!
Oh, I see.
Genesis Merge!
Genesis... Merge.
Engrave!
Aquarion!
[MAIA]
I'm sorry, Akira.
I know it's wrong, but...
It... It feels...
...so wonderful!
[MAIA, SUBETE]
Ressho!
Give me power!
That foolish puppet!
[MAIA gasping]
Maia?
[NESTA giggles]
Silly girl.
Nesta... No...
She hasn't the
first idea what it costs
to wield my power.
Such a desperate move
on her part.
I'm almost moved to pity.
An artificial body like
this could never contain me.
It's far too unstable
to be a proper vessel.
At least, like this.
On the other hand,
raising her power to my level
would make her the perfect
repository for my essence.
Wait! Stop!
What the hell do you think
you're doing to Maia?!
[SUBETE groans]
[SUBETE coughs]
[NESTA]
Oh, dear.
Harbor a lingering affection
for the puppet, did we?
You ought not push
yourself quite so much.
Your friend Akira isn't
the only one short on time.
I'm afraid both
of you are doomed.
No! You lie!
Now... Let's get our
little soirée back on track.
Sorry. This party's
about to be over.
Akira! You've got
to destroy this machine!
[MAIA]
Impale Subete.
Don't give a thought to me!
I'll die if it lets you
save the world!
It's your only chance! Do it!
Maia...
Are you out of your mind?
You seem worried.
Is it because in a physical body
you can actually be killed?
You whore! This was your plan?
None of us will walk away
from this unscathed,
not even you.
You're a puppet! Nothing more!
[SAKURAKO]
What?
[SHOKO] The Black Aquarions
are on the move again!
Not good! We can't
get everyone out in time!
[KOKONE]
I'll deal with them!
[SAKURAKO] Kikogami?
What are you thinking?
[KOKONE] I can at least
b-buy us some time.
That's crazy!
You'll be one Vector
against an entire horde!
[MALE STAFF MEMBER 21A]
Another victim here!
[FEMALE STAFF MEMBER 21A]
And a lot more on the way!
[MALE DOCTOR 21A]
Right. Just a moment, please!
[MALE STAFF MEMBER 21B]
Our team's at the ready!
C'mon, guys.
What's with all the noise?
[MAIA]
Don't falter, Akira!
We're running out of time.
It's all I can do to keep
her trapped inside me!
Her power's... overwhelming me!
Maia, no...
[MAIA] Run us through!
You're the Savior, damn it!
[AKIRA gasps]
If we wait any longer,
more people will die.
[AKIRA] I...
I'll save the entire world!
Including you!
That's not possible.
Well I don't believe that!
Please, Akira.
If you end this,
you'll never have to fly
another Vector again, I swear.
You... You won't
have to disappear!
I'm begging you! Please!
[MAIA] If the alternative
is forgetting you,
then I'd honestly
rather be dead.
Do this for me.
[AKIRA]
Don't give in to that bullshit!
[AKIRA growling]
[MAIA]
Damn it, Akira!
[crying]
It's too late to save me,
but you can still
save everyone else!
I can't. I don't have it in me.
I'm not a savior.
Akira...
[NESTA]
It's over.
[SHOKO]
No!
It's n-not gonna work.
[TSUTOMU] Now why you gotta
go and make my woman cry?
[KOKONE gasps]
Ts-Tsutomu?
[M.J.B.K. laughing]
[TSUTOMU]
Come on, Hayato. Akira.
Think it's time we merged.
Genesis Merge!
Roar, Aquarion!
[TSUTOMU] Dude. That look
on your face has gotta go.
[TSUTOMU] I mean,
I know there's nothing fun
about what's happening
right now, but damn.
[SHOKO]
Tsutomu!
[TSUTOMU]
We have to laugh, man.
Especially in times like this.
That's the
Comedian's Philosophy!
I'm gonna bring 'em back.
Every smile in the world.
Tsutomu. Thank you.
[M.J.B.K. laughing]
[TSUTOMU, AKIRA, HAYATO]
Amaterasu!
[M.J.B.K. laughing]
[MAIA] This light is
so... bright. Beautiful.
It gives me strength.
This goes no further.
[NESTA]
Impossible!
[TSUTOMU] I wonder...
Was I able to make Shoko smile?
Seriously.
Girl's got a fantastic one.
I love it.
He did it!
Tsutomu, you beautiful
bastard, you did it!
[KARAN, KOKONE sobbing]
Damn it.
You said...
You were gonna
bring the smiles back.
Where's mine?
Where's my smile?
[SHOKO sobbing]
[KARAN] I just got a gig
for a bonsai-growing show!
[KOKONE]
That's awesome!
[HAYATO]
I may not know how pop idols
normally do it, Karan,
but something tells me
a late-night program
aimed at old people
won't exactly be
your ticket to fame.
[KARAN] I'm trying to reach as
wide an audience as possible,
not just you!
[HAYATO]
Episode 22.
[KOKONE] "Listen! The Voice
Calling Out to You."
I can r-reach out, too!