[SOUGON grunts]
Summer! In all its glory!
[TSUTOMU]
One, two... three!
Well, that settles things.
The winners of our one
day, one night vacation:
Maia, Karan, Akira,
and, last but not
least, yours truly!
So, are you excited?
No, this is merely
an assignment.
But I'm looking
forward to the ocean.
[AKIRA]
Kokone Kikogami.
[gasps]
Would you prefer to go?
Huh?!
What?
I could feel your
passionate gaze.
Take my place instead, please!
It-It wasn't p-passionate
at all. I... uh...
Why not make it
an all-girls trip?
Use the opportunity to bond.
Are you s-sure?
If you went, you could
spend time with Maia.
You don't m-mind?
No. I'm the Savior, after all.
On second thought,
I think I'll stay here.
Meow?
[TSUTOMU, SHOKO]
Huh?
Ah! I'm sorry. N-Now I
feel like I'm intruding.
But, Maia, you looked
so excited to go.
[MAIA]
Nuh-uh!
Ooh, sparks are flying!
My, my, whatever shall we do?
One more time, so there're
no hard feelings.
Rock, Paper, Scissors.
One, two, three!
[SOUGON] In times past,
humanity was at one
with the world of truth.
but the written word,
for all we prospered from it,
wrought incalculable suffering.
[ANNOUNCER]
Your attention, please.
The train bound for Takao
will be arriving shortly
at Platform One.
For your safety, please remain
behind the yellow line.
[SHOKO]
Good morning, Maia!
You guys're late!
[gasps] G-Good morning!
Hi...
[MAIA]
Remember: surveillance mission.
But that means more than
just watching Akira.
I have to get to know
this Verbalism Club
and their specific
interpersonal dynamics!
[SHOKO]
Look, there's no need to sulk
just 'cause Akira
didn't come along.
You and Kokone may be
rivals, but play nice.
Rivals?
Well, you're both totally
going after Akira, right?
How'd you know?
N-No, it isn't like
that. You're wrong!
[KARAN]
Sorry I'm late!
[SHOKO gasps]
That hat is ridiculously cute.
Thanks, my mom got it for me.
[KARAN]
See you soon, Mom!
Don't worry, ma'am.
I promise I'll take care of your
daughter as if she were my own!
But that's a big deal!
Sh-She's letting you
stay out overnight. Wow!
I had to promise
I'd work extra hard
on my homework and stuff
as soon as I got home!
[SHOKO] Oh, come on! You are
too freaking adorable!
I can't breathe!
[MAIA]
Time to go, ladies.
[KOKONE]
Hold... on.
U-Uh...
[KOKONE]
We're this way.
[TANAKA, TSUTOMU sigh]
This place just isn't the
same without the girls.
Right?
Ahem!
"Oh, who is that pretty
lady in the pink dress?"
"Yeah, she's hot! Mm-mm!"
Lame.
Seems Hayato is
missing in action, too.
[OKAZAKI] That was
basically my only reason
for coming here.
[AKIRA] Have you ladies
decided on something?
[OURA, OKAZAKI gasp]
Miss, it seems your
eyes are all red.
I was up all night!
Of course they're red!
I have bags under my eyes!
Maybe you can help?
Two Red-Eye Lattes
coming right up!
--[OKAZAKI, OURA gushing]
--[SAKURAKO growling]
[TSUTOMU] Yo, Akira, I
gotta ask: Do you swing...
..."that way"?
Which way?
Are you kiddin' me?
I'm trying to find
out whether or not
you're interested in women!
You had a shot at checking out
Maia in a freakin' swimsuit.
And then those chicks just
now. Aren't you interested?
You have the wrong impression.
They interest me.
Huh?
But not just the lady folk.
--I'll rescue anyone in trouble.
--[TSUTOMU] Uh-huh.
--For I--!
--Heard it before.
[MAIA gasps]
[SHOKO gasps]
We got the place to ourselves.
[SHOKO giggles]
C'mon in, ladies!
The water's fine!
[KARAN gasps]
[giggles]
Now, that's a great idea!
[yelps]
What's wrong? An ambush?
[KOKONE] You're naked!
Where's your s-swimsuit?
Show yourself, you coward!
[KOKONE]
Excuse me, M-Maia?
Y-You don't have sandals.
Do your feet hurt?
No, it feels neat.
[BOTH gasp]
What's this? The
sea is advancing!
Wait. Um. Y-You
mean the w-waves?
I guess.
Waves, huh?
[MAIA]
They're waves!
[SHOKO]
They sure are.
Where's the sea stop
and the wave start?
[KARAN]
Whoa. That's deep.
[KOKONE]
Um.
You ever think m-maybe
the whole ocean is a wave?
I've only seen it in videos.
[gasps]
[SHOKO, KARAN giggle]
Hey, stop it!
We call this "splashing"!
Hey! That's enough.
You two, stop tha--
[SHOKO]
Run away! Let's book it, Karan!
[MAIA]
Halt! Kikogami!
Come and fight by my side!
Sure! You got it!
[GIRLS shouting, laughing]
I apologize for my tardiness.
[SAKURAKO]
Welcome!
You've worked so hard.
I'm grateful. Thanks!
Careful. You might catch a cold.
Man. I barely got any
reaction from Hayato.
And after I went
to all the trouble
of giving you men what you want!
[TSUTOMU] That's not really
how it works, boss.
[SAKURAKO]
Hm?
You can't just put
it all out there!
But, thank you, though!
Now, a swimsuit covered
by a parka or beach towel?
Your bare flesh gets
revealed as you slip them
off your body then sensuously
slink into the water.
Maidenly bashfulness is
required to make it uber sexy!
Bashfulness, huh?
I seem to have lost that
somewhere along the way.
[AKIRA]
Are swimsuits really that great?
Duh! They're true justice!
Justice? Is that so?
[TSUTOMU]
You're a bikini man?
Who can blame ya? Me, too!
[SAKURAKO sighs]
[HAYATO]
This is stupid.
[SHOKO]
You can say anything.
So long as you use the
kanji radical for clothing!
Sleeves!
Hakama!
Nudity!
What's radical clothing
got to do with it?
[MAIA, KOKONE, SHOKO giggle]
[KOKONE] This is the
radical for clothing.
This one's too hard.
Let's do something easier.
You'll never beat an M.J.B.K.
with an attitude like that!
How's that considered training?
It sh-sharpens our
critical thinking.
Someone's gettin'
some kanji homework
when we head back!
Huh?! No thanks. I'll just
use my Verbalism Ability!
Uh-huh.
Maybe we should put
that ability to the test!
Now stand up, face the
sea, look deep inside,
and shout out the name
of the one you love!
[KARAN]
What for?
[SHOKO] Verbalism is all
about harnessing the power
that lays dormant in kanji!
Which means if you want
the absolute best results,
it only makes sense
for you to choose a word
you can put some
extra "oomph" into!
In fact, all three of you
should give it a shot!
And, if we're lucky,
we might even
see some sparks fly!
[MAIA]
Master Sougon!
If I yelled Master's
name at the ocean,
they'd realize I was a spy.
I nearly fell into
her ingenious trap.
Well played, Shoko.
You'll do it, too, won't ya?
Unfortunately, I don't
have Verbalism Ability,
so it would be pointless.
But never mind all that.
You try!
[KARAN] I don't feel
that way about anyone!
[SHOKO]
Oh, come on, are you sure?
Ah! Maybe someone from
back at the Club?
[KARAN]
Uh...
My mother...?
[KOKONE, MAIA, SHOKO]
Huh?
I said it! I'm done!
One more time, louder!
I don't wanna!
[SHOKO]
Ta-dah!
[MAIA]
Shirobaco lunch boxes!
What, is that all?
There a problem?
Why are you getting
offended, Maia?
Now then, all together, girls!
[GIRLS]
Thank you for the food!
Oh, wow!
So, why are you even
involved with DEAVA?
I was originally
scouted out because
they thought I might have
Verbalism Ability, but--
We have the results
from your second exam.
I'm afraid it shows
conclusively you have
no aptitude for the gift.
[gasps]
I'm very sorry.
But to your credit,
making it this far
without it is impressive.
Doesn't matter.
There's got to be
something else I can do.
Let me help!
I started working at Shirobaco
as a part time
waitress that day.
Before long, I was an operator.
So the part time job came first?
As for me.
I didn't even know
there was a cr-crisis
until the M.J.B.K.'s
started running wild.
But Sh-Shoko was already
on board, at that point!
Yeah, for all the good I did.
You're our Ace in
the Hole, Kokone.
[gasps]
[SHOKO]
And of course, you, too, Maia.
[KARAN]
What about me?
[SHOKO] You still need
to study your kanji!
[KARAN]
Not this again!
C-Can't sleep?
No.
[KOKONE]
I d-didn't join up with DEAVA
to s-save the world.
[MAIA]
Huh?
[KOKONE] I m-mean, we
need t-to do something
about the M.J.B.K.'s, and
I'm g-glad we fight them.
But I want to be an actress.
Th-That's the real
reason I joined.
I know I may not
seem c-cut out for it.
[MAIA]
An actress?
I'm tr-training my voice.
Honing its power. M-Maybe
that way... my dream...
...will c-come true. I h-hope.
And you, M-Maia?
What made you decide to stay
and f-fight alongside
p-perfect strangers?
I don't really know.
[gasps]
[MAIA]
Monitor Akira Kaibuki.
There's been no further
word since Master Sougon
gave me that order.
And to that end, I fight
alongside the enemy.
Is that what he'd
have wanted me to do?
I don't know.
Um, d-does it have
to do with Akira?
[MAIA gasps]
[KOKONE] I-I'm sorry!
That's none of my business.
Goo-Goodnight!
[KOKONE gasps]
What about you?
Why do you keep trying
to get close to Akira?
You're always looking at him
more than all the others.
Just like in our last battle.
It was obvious you only
cared about performing
a Merge with him.
What am I missing?
[gasps, whimpers]
[MAIA] Answer me, and
be completely honest.
What exactly are you plotting?
I-I d-don't
actually know myself.
I've just f-found
myself watching him.
My heart beats f-faster
and my mind g-goes blank.
Like a sickness?
[gasps] I s-suppose.
I misunderstood. I apologize.
It's all right. So,
um, wh-what about you?
Huh?
I mean, you w-watch him,
too. S-So, how come?
Uh-- I... Because I'm sick, too.
Oh. I s-see.
[TSUTOMU laughs]
Behold the glory!
[AKIRA]
What's that now?
At long last, I'm done!
I used an Aquariphone app
to make this bitchin' image!
[SAKURAKO]
Not too shabby!
[laughing]
Here, let me see.
Oh, yeah. Cool! There, deleted!
No way!
I stayed up all freaking
night working on that!
C'mon! I wanna see
sexy girls in swimsuits!
Ridiculous.
I guess there's only
one choice then.
Don't toy with me.
Well it's not like we have
any customers anyway.
If I let you go now,
you just might make it!
[TSUTOMU]
Miss Sakurako! You're my savior!
[AKIRA]
You called?
You're going, too, aren't you?
Why not? If swimsuits
are that amazing.
I must experience them
myself. Because, I am--
Heck, yeah!
Watch out, summer sun,
'cause here I come!
Ah-Ah-choo!
Brr! What gives? It's freezin'!
Snow?
[SOUGON]
Verbalize. Rejoice.
Today I deign to set you free!
[ANNOUNCER]
The express train to Tokyo
will be arriving
shortly at Platf--
[SAKURAKO]
Bizarre weather phenomena
have turned summer on end
across the hemisphere.
Just look at this
word corrosion rate!
[TSUTOMU] It's obviously
an M.J.B.K! Let's roll!
Verbalize.
[SAKURAKO]
Wait!
[KENTO]
Are all three of them going out?
Hang on a sec.
We'll send in two recon units!
If we throw all
three machines at him,
we'll be done in no time!
The sooner we wrap things up...
...the sooner I
see dem skivvies!
[SAKURAKO]
That's your reason?
[SHOKO]
I knew it was an M.J.B.K!
Yeah. The four of us
are safe for now.
We'll wait. I suppose
the rest is up to you.
[KOKONE sneezes]
Karan, a-are you cold?
Freezing.
Akira and the others've
launched and are on their way.
We need to hold our position
here until the blizzard passes.
[gasps]
[thuds]
[KOKONE]
Karan?
Karan!
[MAIA]
Karan Umanagi!
[M.J.B.K. 5A]
Natsu!
Natsu. Natsu. Natsu.
Natsu. Natsu!
[HAYATO]
That's him.
[TSUTOMU]
Mergin' time! For the swimsuits!
--C'mon already! Yeah, yeah!
--[HAYATO] Genesis Merge. Roar!
[TSUTOMU, HAYATO, AKIRA]
Aquarion!
[gasps]
[AKIRA]
What?
[TSUTOMU]
Crap!
[HAYATO, AKIRA,
TSUTOMU grunting]
[M.J.B.K. 5A]
Natsu! Natsu!
[panting]
She's s-so cold.
Hypothermia might be setting in.
If we don't do something,
she might die!
Hang in there!
Don't!
If you move her suddenly, it
could put strain on her heart.
We've got to do something!
If only we could wrap
her in a blanket or,
even better, find a way
to heat this place!
[MAIA]
I'll get one!
[KOKONE]
You can't! You might get l-lost!
[SHOKO]
It's too dangerous!
[TSUTOMU]
Hey! It won't move at all!
[HAYATO grunts]
Nothing works.
[AKIRA]
Frozen solid.
No! Dammit!
I wanna see those
swimsuits! Swim! Suits!
You're still fixated on that?
[TSUTOMU]
Those swimsuits need saving!
Huh? Would you
please be serious?
I'm super-mega serious!
[HAYATO]
No, you're an idiot!
[SAKURAKO growls] Cut it out,
that's an order! Now!
No. Domon's taking
this incredibly seriously.
[SAKURAKO]
Huh?
I have proof.
Damn it all! Swimsuits
are at stake, here!
[chanting] Swimsuits.
Swimsuits...
Look!
But how?
Tsutomu Domon is melting
it with his passion.
All this for
something so trivial?
This is not even
remotely trivial!
How long're you gonna
keep lyin' to yourself?
Say it!
Say that you absolutely
adore swimsuits!
[HAYATO]
Don't lump me in with you!
[TSUTOMU]
No way! There's no denying it!
You can try to act cool.
But you were totally
ogling the Commander
out of the corner of your eye!
Were you really?
[HAYATO]
That's just... ludicrous.
S-So cold.
[MAIA]
I'm sorry.
[SHOKO]
Maia.
Everything inside
was already gone.
[SHOKO]
That's not your fault!
Now come in from the cold!
[panting]
Karan, no.
All right, I've got a plan.
Let's get Karan out of her suit.
I'm gonna help out, too!
Oh! M-Me, too.
[MAIA]
Karan. I won't let you die!
[M.J.B.K. 5A]
Natsu!
Swimsuit time. Swimsuit time!
You're wrong. Okay?
I'm not like that!
[AKIRA]
Hayato Kujyo.
No one wants to follow a person
who makes excuses
for who they are.
Swimsuits today, who
knows what tomorrow.
I'll save them all!
Can you say the same?
Huh?
[TSUTOMU]
Hayato!
[AKIRA] Give voice to
your burning feelings!
[HAYATO]
Yes. My burning feelings.
Say it loud!
[HAYATO]
I...
[rumbling]
[HAYATO]
I... I...
I love the look of
a school swimsuit!
Oh, what a lovely fetish!
I've received your soaring
spirit. It burns bright!
[AKIRA, TSUTOMU, HAYATO]
Phoenix!
[SAKURAKO] The phoenix
of sweaty, man passion!
[KENTO]
So hot right now!
[M.J.B.K. 5A]
Natsu!
The heat of our passion
will melt you down to nothing!
For we are...
...the swimsuit saviors!
[ALL]
A passionate man's blood...
...remains hot!
[TSUTOMU, AKIRA, HAYATO]
Fire!
[M.J.B.K. 5A]
Natsu! Natsu! Natsu! Natsu!
In all it's glory!
It's so warm.
[MAIA]
Can you hear me, Karan?
You okay?
Hi, sleepy head!
Did the cold freeze
everyone's tops off?
[KOKONE, MAIA, SHOKO
giggle, sob]
It's warm again.
I g-guess the boys won!
Thank goodness she was fine.
[TSUTOMU] Move it! Move it!
Move it! Move it! Move it!
We're off to see
our bathing beauties!
[HAYATO]
Wait for us!
[AKIRA]
Nobody's here.
[HAYATO]
Why not?
[TSUTOMU groans]
Hayato! Akira!
Swimsuits!
Hey, Akira! Hayato!
Kaibuki?
Yes. Let's.
[laughs]
--[AKIRA grunting] Got you!
--[HAYATO laughing]
[TSUTOMU yelps]
It's salty!
Oh, wow!
Watching the sea roll
under the sunset?
I wish I could have gone, too!
You should keep
the school swimsuit
limited to use at Shirobaco.
S-S-School swimsuit?
Nothing for you to worry about.
Next episode, I'm gonna
give it everything I've got!
[KOKONE] M-Manager's finally
entering the battle?
[AKIRA]
Episode Six!
[SAKURAKO]
"Light up! Your Strength!"
[AKIRA] One more thing.
Gym shorts are off limits.
Fine, I won't wear 'em.