--[banging]
--[SUBETE] Open up!
--Let me outta here!
I know you can hear me!
Do you have any idea who I am?
[growls]
[SOUGON]
I assume you are familiar
with the concept of
"annoyance," Subete?
In Kanji, it is
written as "may fly."
An apt description for
your current behavior.
May fly?
Father?
[SUBETE grunting] Let go
of me! What are you doing?
Father! Tell them to unhand me!
I'm only trying to rescue
Maia from the enemy!
Silence the boy.
[groans]
[SOUGON]
Drive.
I spoke with Mr. Hayashi.
According to him, Maia is
there on your orders, Father.
Is that the truth?
And what if it is?
[SUBETE] But! Why would
you do that to her?
That's not where she belongs!
Where Maia belongs is
not for you to decide.
[SOUGON] The pilot of the
Red Vector must be verified.
Judging from his
performance thus far,
it is more than possible we
have found the chosen one.
[gasps]
[SOUGON] It is imperative
that we know for certain
one way or the other.
[SUBETE]
Impossible!
I reject the very notion!
Who is this nobody
to challenge me?
I am the chosen one!
[SOUGON] In times past,
humanity was at one
with the world of truth.
but the written word,
for all we prospered from it,
wrought incalculable suffering.
[SQUAD MEMBERS panting]
[SECURITY GUARDS grunt, gasp]
[HAYASHI]
"The river flows, constant,
unceasing, the current
surging ever forward.
The foam crowning
stagnant water vanishes,
reappears, churning in
and out of existence
on an endless cycle.
So it is with people
and the monuments
they erect to their vanity.
Here one moment, gone the next.
A dwelling may burn to ash,
only to be rebuilt.
A large house crumbles,
becomes a hovel.
A man dies at dawn,
another is born by twilight.
In this, we are
as a great current,
or the foam on stagnant water.
I know not whence the newborn
comes, nor wither go the dead."
[SQUAD COMMANDER]
Target sighted! Open fire!
Verbalize.
[HAYASHI]
"When all is impermanence,
for what do we toil?
For whom do we trouble our
minds with temporary things?
Why do fragile and inconstant
baubles delight our eye?"
Ruin.
[HAYASHI] "From first to last,
we cannot deny that dweller
and dwelling are no
different than dew
and the fragile blossoms
of the morning glory
upon which it lights.
Both possess only the briefest
aspiration to exist at all."
[SQUAD MEMBER F groans]
[HAYASHI] "Should the dew fall,
and the blossom linger,
its pedals will yet
wilt in the sun.
Should the blossom wilt
and the dew remain,
night will see
the twinkling gone."
[SOUGON]
Quoting the Hojoki?
[HAYASHI]
I'm quite fond of it, actually.
[SOUGON]
Hmph.
[HAYASHI] You've always
hated it, of course.
[SQUAD COMMANDER grunts]
This is Delta Squad.
The mission is a failure.
I'm the only one left.
[SQUAD COMMANDER whimpers]
[SQUAD COMMANDER screams]
I tried to warn 'em
going up against
Sougon and his Book of Verbalism
wouldn't be a
straightforward matter.
Why won't they
ever listen to you?
Idiots. They should heed
the warnings by now.
Instead, they rush
in like always.
[SAKURAKO] I can't blame
the government for wanting
a speedy resolution
to this mess.
[KENTO] And of course,
we're beholden to them
for continued funding
and manpower.
'S not exactly a walk in
the park for us peons.
The upper echelon bean counters
must be doing an audit.
I hope they don't think we're
a "budgetary black hole."
We're barely scraping
by as it is.
[HAYASHI]
A barrier, huh?
[SOUGON] It would appear
the Vectors are not all
Sakurako Soda had the
audacity to take from me.
Steal your heart, did she?
[SOUGON]
Hmph.
The Logos Monument.
Excavated together with
the Book of Verbalism.
[SAKURAKO] As long as we
keep that artifact onsite,
Sougon can't use his precious
book anywhere near our base.
He's powerful, no question.
But the monument blocks him from
attacking us in the real world.
So it's a bit like
a game of chicken.
No side can make a move
against the other.
[SAKURAKO] I've grown into
such an awful person.
What kind of monster uses
children to fight their battles?
While hiding out
safe and sound, no less.
[KENTO] You're hardly the
only one guilty of that.
You've just described
everyone involved.
[SAKURAKO] Is that the best
you can do to console me?
[SAKURAKO] Fact of the matter
is, I'm not doing enough.
[HAYATO]
One more time.
Let's go over the specific
capabilities of each vector.
Kaibuki's Vector One
is a multipurpose type
with a variety of uses.
Tsukigane's Vector Two
has superior power,
giving it a bit
more maneuverability.
Kikogami's Vector Three
primarily disrupts
the enemy and
provides rear support.
'Stomu's Vector Four is our
tank: the heavy attacker.
It specializes in
hit and run tactics.
My own Vector Five
is the fastest:
a high speed, range
of mobility type.
Finally, Uminagi's Vector Six.
The strengths of this unit
are Ambush and Reconnaissance.
Why do I get stuck with
the unlucky number?
Four's bad news.
Why do we use
Vector Two so often?
With Vector One
always in the field,
it doesn't really contribute
any unique functions.
[HAYATO] Because if the reports
are anything to go by,
Aquarion is, for
whatever reason,
more stable in a Merge
with you and Akira.
[KARAN] "Must be nice." That's
what you're thinking, right?
What? N-No! N-Not at all!
[KARAN]
Aw, c'mon! Don't be embarrassed!
Celebrate your puberty!
Yeah, says the one
person in the room
furthest from it!
--[KARAN] Don't be a jerk!
--Ow!
Why do we have to refer
to them by number?
[HAYATO]
That's not good enough for you?
Hey, let's hear 'im out.
You've got some
alternatives, right?
[HAYATO] Can't hurt to
consider them, I suppose.
What have you got?
Rejected.
[gasps]
No offense or anything,
but that's not
nearly cute enough.
And if Akira changes
the name of his,
the rest of us have to
follow suit and rename ours.
Uh. I don't m--
I don't mind being Savior T-Two.
That would be my name!
[TSUTOMU]
Can't you both just share it?
[KARAN] If they're doing
that, I'm going with...
No chance in hell. Ugh.
What do you people
think Vectors are?
[KARAN]
Ew.
Hey. Heading home?
Yep.
Have a good one.
Bye-bye!
S-See you tomorrow.
[KARAN] "Savior Go"
totally isn't happening.
[TSUTOMU] What goes into
makin' a guy like Akira?
Like, how was he raised?
Master ordered me to keep
a watchful eye on him.
But so far, my observations are
limited to what I see here.
[KARAN]
That reminds me, Mr. Hayato.
My mother has kind of a
special request for you.
[HAYATO]
A request?
[KARAN]
Uh-huh!
I don't dare go to Master
Sougon with so little intel.
[MAIA]
Leaving early!
Wait! You're pulling
this again? Maia!
That's right, Akira.
I'm going to find out
what makes you tick.
[gasps] What on Earth
is that creature?
No, not Earth.
Clearly not indigenous
to this community,
or even to this solar system.
So, where is it from?
[gasps]
[MAIA grunts]
[growls]
[MAIA]
Exterminate!
[KIDS shouting]
Hey, you! Stop bein' a bully!
Who do you think you are, lady?
What is wrong with you, larvae?
Why are you defending
this hideous beast!
--Let go of me! Ow!
--[sighs]
[MAIA]
This must be...
[AKIRA] Quit dragging
your feet. Come inside.
We'll put on some tea.
But how could he have known?
Remember: it is not the ink
that abides in your brush.
The bristles must be
permeated by your soul!
[AKIRA] That's my grandpa.
He teaches calligraphy.
[SHIZUKA] Well, I have to say,
it's not like our boy
to bring friends home.
So a cute little thing
like you is unheard of.
[AKIRA]
Technically, I didn't bring her.
She's here because
she followed me.
[SHIZUKA chuckles]
Pay no attention, my dear,
he's happy as a
clam to have you.
Consider our door open any
old time you'd like to drop by.
I'll consider it.
[coughs]
Oh, no, I brewed it too strong!
Guess she's picky.
You dirty rat, poisoning
me in your own home.
[door scrapes]
My thanks. A token.
[SUBETE GUARD 6A]
Oh. That's not...
Now, to have a proper
word with my father!
[SAKURAKO] It's been quite
a while since I've come here.
This is the source
of the M.J.B.K.s.
No doubt in my mind.
I have to do something.
Anything to make
their fight easier.
It's the least I owe them.
[alarm beeps]
[SAKURAKO]
Hm. Well, it was worth a shot.
I haven't been his
secretary in years.
[yelps]
Ugh, ow, dammit.
[SUBETE] Terribly sorry!
Are you all right?
You're... Miss Sakurako?
Subete.
[TSUTOMU]
Showtime, folks!
For my first trick,
I shall make the contents
of this delectable oden vanish
in the blink of an eye...
...into the dark
recesses of my belly!
[sighs] Looks like
nobody's favorite
"online comedian" is at it
again with the oden schtick.
Poor bastard.
View count's so low
it's almost sad.
You still not havin' any luck
gettin' through to Sakurako?
I don't know what to do.
I've been shootin' her
texts for an hour.
[KENTO]
Hm...
Uh?!
[SAKURAKO] Easy there,
Subete. People are looking.
I... I'm sorry.
I never imagined your
reasons for stealing
Father's vectors was so...
I mean, upholding your invalid
mother's dearest wish...
Yes, Mother.
[SUBETE]
She wanted to see one so badly.
I can only imagine what
that must have been like
for you--such a caring daughter!
Willing... Willing to move
heaven and earth for the woman
who gave birth to you!
[SAKURAKO]
Least I could do.
Who in their right mind
falls for a story like that?
Is she... Is she still
with us, or, uh...?
Oh, she's great! Fit as
a fiddle, truth be told.
Seems the sight of
a vector in action
is just the cure
for what ails ya!
Ah! That's wonderful news!
I'd planned to return
them all along.
If only I had a better
home security system.
See, a burglar broke in while I
was running errands and made off
with the darn things before
I could bring them back.
Oh, my! Sounds so violating!
[SAKURAKO] Well, it's not
like I can lay everything
out on the table and tell
him I'm using the vectors,
now is it?
[SUBETE]
Now I'm almost sure:
Maia's with those reprobates
responsible for the theft!
If only I could probe
a little further.
Trouble is, I don't dare
let the world know
I piloted a vector into battle.
[SAKURAKO, SUBETE
laugh nervously]
[SUBETE]
Sakurako?
[SAKURAKO]
Yes?
[SUBETE] I'm sorry for
thinking poorly of you.
[SAKURAKO]
Don't worry about it.
[SUBETE]
No. I oughtta have
given you the benefit
of the doubt.
When I heard that
you'd taken the vectors,
I assumed you'd betrayed us.
You deserved better of me.
Period. I'm sorry.
I'm the one who's sorry.
What did I expect
everyone to believe?
[SUBETE]
Let me make it up to you.
Anything you want, it's yours!
Huh?
And don't be conservative!
I have this! Makes the
whole world my oyster!
[SAKURAKO]
Uh... Ha...
Yes. I've seen this.
[RANKO] You can't deny those
dance moves are on point.
And Karan's angelic vocals
are 100% not auto tuned.
[HATANO]
Uh-huh.
Yes, I know. Ugh.
The ad only played locally.
And I'm pretty sure
the only people
who've seen it
are the film crew.
That being said!
Mr. Hatano, your support
among young voters
is the highest in the
country! Kids worship you!
If you put this track
in your next commercial,
it'll be huge for you and her!
Huh?
My Karan is a voice actress now.
Wouldn't the perfect debut for
her be as the voice of youth
for your whole campaign?
Excuse me.
Yes?
Granted, I'm not as up to speed
on the "young idol" phenomenon
as someone in my position
probably should be but, uh,
grabbing the hearts and minds
of a whole generation?
Seems a pretty ambitious goal
for this stage of the game.
Well, if you're gonna dream,
you've gotta dream big.
Maybe, but you've
got to be realistic
about the industry.
The fact of the matter is,
very few newcomers last.
Most pop idols amount
to a flash in the pan
before simply disappearing.
Same with voice actors.
It sounds harsh, but
that's just the reality.
I feel like I've seen
a lot of young talent
ground up and spit out.
Fame is a fickle bitch.
Pardon the language,
ma'am, but...
I don't wanna see
that happen to Karan.
If she's in this
for the notoriety,
she's in it for
the wrong reasons.
What's important is letting
her talent be fulfilling
in and of itself.
You're adorable.
Yep. Still bitter.
[SHIZUKA] He said give you these
to help with the aftertaste.
Huh?
[SHIZUKA]
He doesn't like to show it,
but he's actually
a very nice boy.
Has he... Has he
always been like that?
I mean, with the
whole "savior" thing?
Since the day he was born,
believe it or not.
We can't even tell you why
he's hung up on the idea
of playing the hero--
it's just been part of him
from the beginning. I can
tell you this much, however.
If he can help,
that boy never shows
the slightest sign
of hesitation.
He's gifted with the
knowledge of what to do
in any situation where
someone needs rescuing.
He just knows what
to do? Must be nice.
[SUBETE]
Hey, c'mon! Don't hold back!
[SUBETE laughs]
[SUBETE]
Oh, you're in for it now!
Tornado... Strike!
Yeah!
You sure it's okay
for you to do this?
[SUBETE]
Do what?
[SAKURAKO] I don't know,
mingle with the commoners?
[SUBETE] But I'm enjoying
myself immensely!
I think of it as giving
the people a gift.
Who wouldn't want
to be in my presence?
That sense of superiority
is gonna get your ass kicked.
--[BOY 6D] Bye-Bye!
--[MOTHER] Thank you both
--so much!
[SAKURAKO] Still the
same old Subete, I see.
Huh?
I always questioned whether
that environment
was good for you.
[SAKURAKO] Your luncheon
with President Ringosberg
is set for two PM.
After that, you've got
a quorum meeting at three.
[SUBETE]
Daddy!
You'll be so proud of me,
I came in first place!
[SOUGON]
Throw the intruder out, please.
Excuse me?
[SOUGON]
This is a place of business.
I am decidedly not
running a daycare.
[SUBETE]
But, Daddy! I'm sorry!
[SUBETE] I certainly had
my share of disappointments.
But... at the very least,
I didn't suffer them alone.
And having faith got us
through the worst of it.
Believing always pays
you back in strength.
In the end, I knew in my heart
Father would be proud of me.
I understood that
I was the chosen one.
In the grand scheme of
things, I had a place.
Life can be tough, but being
special makes it all worthwhile.
Call it what it is, Subete.
You do nothing on your own and
rely on others for everything.
Huh?
That's just sad.
[crashing]
What was that?
[M.J.B.K. 6A]
Dan!
[SOUGON]
Hm.
[TSUTOMU grunting, panting]
[TSUTOMU] Tell me you're
getting all of this.
[beeping]
[KOKONE] Um. Maybe?
The internet's d-down.
[KARAN] I'm here with
the hot young senator
everyone's talking
about, Mr. Hatano.
I question the wisdom of getting
her involved in politics.
I get that an actor has to
follow the work, but still.
[RANKO]
I know. It's boring.
But her delivery!
Ugh. Are you kidding me?!
[AKIRA, MAIA panting]
[CROWD yelling]
[EMPLOYEE 6A]
Everyone, remain calm!
The elevators are
temporarily out of service.
Please don't panic!
[grunts]
[OPERATOR 1B] Vector units One
and Two, system link complete.
[OPERATOR 1A]
Adjustments to magnetic
alignment confirmed.
Activation....
[OPERATOR 1B]
All warp gate generation
field systems are "go."
[SHOKO] I'm afraid the commander
won't make it back in time.
I'll stand in for her
until she gets here,
but don't expect miracles.
Not the sort of
thing that inspires
confidence in your pilots.
Let's do this.
[MAIA]
Verbalize.
[CROWD screaming]
[SAKURAKO]
Now I'm the a-hole.
What was I saying about
relying on others?
[SUBETE] Miss Sakurako!
I've gotta find my father!
This is chaos.
But if I can get there,
I have a pretty good idea
where to find him.
If there's anyone capable of
bringing her back, it's him!
Nobody else in the world is more
important to me than that girl!
Time to Merge.
[MAIA]
Genesis Merge!
[AKIRA]
Shout!
[MAIA gasps]
What the--?
[KOKONE gasps]
The v-video feed.
We've got a situation.
Father simply misunderstands
my point of view, is all.
If I explain it to him...
[SAKURAKO]
Don't be so naive!
Huh?
[SAKURAKO] This girl is
the most important person
in the world to you, and
the first place you go is
"I'll just talk to Daddy?"
Then what should I do?
[SAKURAKO] I dunno, how
about stop being a baby
and find a way to get
her back yourself!
Be your own man for once!
"Belief pays you
back in strength?"
Sounds like something
a coward says
right before he lets others
do the fighting for him!
It's pathetic!
And trust me. I'm no better.
If anything, I'm actually worse.
I don't just rely on others.
I rely on children.
[gasps]
You're strong enough,
Subete. I know it.
[SUBETE] Thank you.
I needed to hear that.
[gasps]
[SUBETE] You're right.
Belief is meaningless.
If I can't stand
on my own two feet,
what good does it do me?
If I want Maia back,
I have to fight for her.
That's all there is to it!
Wait. Did you just say...?
[MAIA]
Why can't we Merge?
Don't be shy.
Show yourself, M.J.B.K.
[M.J.B.K. 6A]
Dan! Dan! Dan! Da-Dan!
[SUBETE]
I have to grow up!
Time to put away
childish things!
If I ever want
Maia restored to me,
I must first learn
to be worthy of her!
Oh, hell.
Hey, Maia!
Didja know my Nesta timeline
is totally on fire right now?
That sounds like a bad thing.
Traditionally, "on fire"
carries negative connotations,
but youth culture
has turned the phrase
on its head to mean
"amazing," or "awesome."
That's stupid!
Pics of little fur babies
are totes adorbs!
The language is dying.
Or evolving.
[MAIA]
Next: Episode Seven,
"Burn it! The Savior's Flames."
OMG! I can't even!