[CROWD cheering, clapping]
[MALE AUDIENCE MEMBER 10F]
Bravo! Marvelous!
[laughs]
[KOKONE] That was the first
time I ever saw a play.
Since then,
all I've ever wanted...
Kokone sings
like an angel!
She's gonna be a
household name in no time!
[KOKONE] All I've ever dreamed
of was to be an actress.
[SOUGON] In times past,
humanity was at one
with the world of truth.
But the written word,
for all we prospered from it,
wrought incalculable suffering.
[HAYATO] A play?
Not a dramatic reading?
[SAKURAKO] Correct! Our first,
open air theatrical performance!
[SHOKO]
And the venue is terrific!
Get this: we spoke
with the Shinmei Shrine
and they're letting us
use their stage!
[SAKURAKO] Everyone,
study your scripts.
They're super radical!
D'you just say "radical"?
Who talks like that?
Careful. People might
think you're trying to sound
younger than you are.
[SAKURAKO] Moving on!
Let's review the cast list!
[TSUTOMU]
Excuse me?
[KARAN]
Huuuuh?
[KOKONE]
I g-get the th-theme song?
[AKIRA]
Why isn't there a savior?
[MAIA] Um, what country is
this Kaguya a princess of?
[TSUTOMU]
You made me the grandma?
I want to be a prince!
[KARAN] This is an outrage!
Why aren't I the princess?
Karan doesn't play kappa!
[TSUTOMU]
This sucks!
[HAYATO]
Both of you, calm down.
--Oh, put a sock
--Says the guy who
--gets to play a prince!
--in it, big bro!
Suh so, I'm g-guessing all
you want me to do is s-sing?
Right! You have
the job of establishing
the mood of the whole play!
One of the most
important roles, really.
I suh-see.
Hey, manager? Can we
rework the part of the Sage
so he was once a savior?
Wait a minute, I don't
remember a sage being in this.
And, what about Hanako?
I vote Kikogami plays her.
[TSUTOMU] I dunno if
this whole drag thing's
where I want
my comedy career going.
[SAKURAKO]
It softens your appearance.
And besides, it's a good part.
[HAYATO]
With all due respect,
I don't think Kokone
is ready for a lead role.
[AKIRA] Why don't we
ask her if she's ready?
Huh?
What do you say?
Well. I, uh...
I enjoy singing.
B-But what I r-really, um.
What I really
want to do is act!
Okay, we'll give it a shot.
Study the part
backwards and forwards.
The show debuts this weekend.
[ALL]
This weekend?!
[CROWD chattering]
Get your full length
sausages here, folks!
Why watch the play hungry?
Step right up! Autographed
photos of the cast!
Plus! Arts and crafts handmade
by the Verbalism Club!
[SAKURAKO] Ladies and gentlemen,
please take your seats.
The daytime portion of
"Hanako and Princess Kaguya"
will begin presently.
"Bu... But,
Gran-Gran-Grandmother.
What do you, um,
what do you mean?"
"Grandmother, what do you m-mean
there's a l-letter for me?"
[HAYATO]
Try not to worry.
Whatever happens,
we'll cover for you.
Do--Do you think
I-I'll be buh bad?
Don't take it personally.
That's not what I meant.
Honestly, I'm more
concerned about Kaibuki.
[AKIRA]
"Do not fear. I am he
who the good people
call the Savior Sage!"
"I reside high on the
mountaintop cutting bamboo!
I deliver salvation
unto this world!"
"Oh, thank goodness
for you, sir!"
[CROWD laughs]
[HAYATO]
You've got to be kidding!
His first scene and
already he's ad libbing!
So it's okay
if we go off script?
Absolutely not!
But they're eating it up!
[KOKONE] "But grandmother
w-what do you mean there's...
...a l-letter for muh me."
"Hanako? Hanako?
Where've you
gotten off to, dearie?"
[KOKONE]
"Here I am!"
"Ah! So you are, my pet!"
"B-But G-Grandm-mother
w-what do you m-mean
there's a luh-luh-letter
fuh for m-me?"
[CROWD mumbles]
What's happening?
[HAYATO]
This is not good.
You can do it, Kokone!
"Hark, Hanako.
T'is a fine day
for saving people,
don't you think?"
[KOKONE] "Y-Yes, G-Grandfather!
It is induh-deed!"
"This wuh-weather is..."
[CROWD whispers]
[FEMALE AUDIENCE MEMBER 10A]
Well this is awkward.
[FEMALE AUDIENCE MEMBER 10B]
It's gotta be a joke, right?
Uh, I--
I don't understand.
She got through rehearsal.
Ignore them!
You're doing great!
Um. "Yes my dear.
T'was written by
none other than the Prince
of the Moon himself!"
"The... muh m-moon,
you say?
I c-c-can't b-believe it."
[whispers]
Uh. I lost my place.
[whimpers]
[AKIRA] "It is time you know the
truth about the Moon's messiah."
"She is your elder sister."
Why the hell does he
keep improvising?
The princess is the messiah?
I'm a savior, too.
Didn't know we were
going that direction.
We're not!
[AKIRA] "Until such time as you
reached your sixteenth birthday.
It has been my sacred duty
as the Savior Sage
to raise you like
an ordinary, human child!"
[KOKONE] Say something.
He's covering for you!
"Y-Yes! I m-must meet
my elder sister at once!
I shall guh--!"
[BOTH]
Uuh?
[KOKONE] "I sh-shall guh...
go to the moon."
Speak up, please!
I can't hear!
[MALE AUDIENCE MEMBER
10A, 10B chuckle]
[CROWD laughs]
Hey! Stop! She's doing
the best she can!
You guys should
hear her sing at Shirobaco!
Okay, all right.
I'm gonna have to
ask you to come with me.
[TANAKA]
But, I-I'm trying to help!
[KARAN] This is totally
falling apart.
Told you she wasn't ready!
Why does no one listen to me?
"Yea, and to
the moon you shall go.
You've much yet
to learn of your fate!"
[KOKONE gasps]
[KOKONE] "Y-You are right. I
will j-journey there at once!"
[sighs]
We'll just reduce
Kokone's lines.
Share them
among the rest of us.
Are you sure?
[HAYATO] The show certainly
can't go on as it is!
Tsutomu, Karan:
can you take up the slack?
Hell, bro s'not like
we have a choice.
[KARAN]
Yeah, we'll try.
Actually, it's not
really up to us, is it?
Am I wrong?
I'm sorry: it's what's
best for the play.
Not everyone's as
effortlessly gifted as you!
I can't let Kokone go on
humiliating herself!
I-I, uh I'm g-going
out for a while.
[door slides, thuds shut]
[TSUTOMU] Kinda harsh
on her, don't ya think?
I'll say it was.
That's one demerit for you.
We know you mean well, but next
time try to be more sensitive.
[FEMALE AUDIENCE MEMBER 10A]
Who in their right mind
gave that disaster a lead role?
She can barely talk!
[FEMALE AUDIENCE MEMBER 10B]
Amateurs. What can you do?
[FEMALE AUDIENCE MEMBER 10A]
I'm not surprised.
With a name like "Verbalism
Club?" I mean, seriously?
[KOKONE] I'm making
everyone look bad. Oh, god!
[KOKONE]
"Red leather, yellow leather.
Red leather, yellow leather."
"Seven swans swam
across the silver seas."
"Oh. Your huh huh Highness."
"How vuh vuh very...
H-How v-very..."
What's wrong with me?
Why can't I say it?
[cricket chirping]
[gasps]
Wuh... What are you doing here?
[AKIRA] Do you hear
the insects singing?
In-Insects?
[cricket chirping]
Oh yeah. Right.
They sound so... p-pretty.
They're--They're
so small, too.
But we still hear them.
They make so much noise.
Not noise.
Huh?
A leaf bunny? I don't...
It's how they communicate.
[SOUGON]
Verbalize.
Rejoice. Today I deign
to set you free.
[M.J.B.K. 10A]
Oooh!
[crickets chirping]
"Oh my, the p-prince
is vuh very handsome!"
"Do not be deceived, Hanako!
We must go on the attack!"
"Go forth, Prince!
I require the world's
finest truffles from
the world's finest chocolatiers
be brought to me!"
"Yes, I shall do
everything within my power
to procure them."
"But. Your huh highness,
I must implore you."
"My--My sister
and you... are..."
Oh, man. She's even
worse off than earlier.
I'm inclined to think
Hayato was right.
Akira?
I'm not hearing wind.
But look.
[MALE AUDIENCE MEMBER 10C]
Yo. How long we gotta
sit through this?
Sorry. Couldn't hear ya.
[MALE AUDIENCE MEMBER 10C]
I said, how long we gotta
sit through this?
"You cannot give up
now! No, Hanako! No!"
"You must steal his love!
It is not too late for you!"
"I... wuh won't
let you have him!
I can't live without..."
[KARAN] That's weird.
The audience is super
quiet all of a sudden.
[aquariphone buzzing]
Huh? Oh, why now?
--[MAN 10B] Whoa!
--[MAN 10C] Huh.
When did that come down?
[ALL yell]
There's no sound!
[STREET MUSICIAN 10A]
Hm? Aw, c'mon!
Don't do this to me!
Something's off.
What the hell's going on?
[yells]
Hey, watch--!
Oh, no.
Word corrosion rate
is rising, ma'am!
And it's climbing fast!
If it keeps up,
telecommunications and
transit systems will be
at risk of complete collap--!
[grunts]
[MAIA] "We must
keep vigil for Hanako!"
[AKIRA] "She awaits us,
I can sense it.
This old sage
can yet see the truth:
Hanako prays to save the world!"
[MAN 10D] Why is this
the only place with sound?
[MAN 10E]
Yeah. Weird.
This isn't good.
[Aquariphone beeping]
[HAYATO] "Princess. I beg your
forgiveness..."
[SAKURAKO] The word corrosion
rate is still climbing, but why?
[AKIRA] "Come! We must
search for Hanako at once!"
[SAKURAKO]
This doesn't make sense.
How can I hear them?
[HAYATO]
This M.J.B.K. steals sound?
Correct. Our world
is being robbed
of anything perceived
by the ear. However.
For some reason,
this stage is immune.
I suspect our collective
Verbalism ability
has something to do with it.
[KOKONE] S-So that's why
everyone here...
As long as we go on
with the performance
we can keep
the word corrosion rate
from reaching
one hundred percent.
So in a manner of speaking
this is our last bastion.
[SAKURAKO] Right. We'll hold out
until our voices break.
We have to keep t-talking?
But how do we...?
[HAYATO]
By keeping the play going.
It's our best course of action.
[HAYATO] Where are you off to?
This isn't a solo performance!
I'm gonna fight the M.J.B.K.
Good plan. You engage
the enemy while Hayato
and the others
buy us some time here.
That suit you, your Highness?
Sure. Why not?
[KOKONE]
I, uh... I would...
I would like to go with Akira
if that's all right with you.
I w-won't be much use here.
Not w-with the...
way I t-talk.
[SHOKO] Under the circumstances,
voice commands are inoperative.
I'm switching our systems
over to Direct Input Mode
for the time being.
Vectors One and Three,
prepare to launch immediately.
[AKIRA]
Verbalize.
[KOKONE]
[SAKURAKO]
Go! Go!
Oh. That's great.
We have to drag this
train wreck out indefinitely
until the M.J.B.K. is put down.
[MAIA} How are we
supposed to do that?
Going by the script,
we're almost done!
It's okay,
I'm writing new material
to pad out the story.
If we use that up,
ad lib whatever keeps the
audience in their seats.
So I can go off script!
[M.J.B.K. 10A]
Oto? Oto.
Oooooh...
Right, Kikogami: let's go!
Ruh roger!
[M.J.B.K. 10A]
Ooooh...
[KOKONE yelps]
[AKIRA]
Kikogami!
[KOKONE yells]
Damn it. I can't get close.
[SHOKO] Vector Three appears
to have shut down.
Word corrosion is currently
at seventy-four percent.
Areas affected by loss of sound
are cropping up
all over the globe!
Vuh Verbalize.
Verbalize.
Come on! Verbalize!
Wh-Why can't I...
Why can't I do anything?
I m-might as well be on stage.
[M.J.B.K. 10A]
Ooo-to.
Get out of there!
--[M.J.B.K. 10A] Oooh!
--[AKIRA] Dodge it!
[KOKONE screams]
Vital signs
for Vector Three
are at critical and dropping!
Commander, if she keep
this up, I fear the worst!
I can't. I c-can't
d-do anything!
[yells]
[KOKONE]
I'm powerless. I'm...
[KOKONE] I'm useless.
Abso-lutely useless.
Your voice.
[groans]
Akira, is that...?
Wh-What about my voice?
Not noise.
[KOKONE] I get it. When I
don't speak from the heart,
my words trip
all over themselves.
It's just random noise.
Because I'm not communicating.
Who am I?
A useless little girl
who needs everything
spelled out for her.
Akira, I...
...love you!
[KARAN]
She's singing.
Kokone.
"Do you hear? Is that
our sweet Hanako singing?"
"Yes! No doubt, that is
our dear girl's voice!"
[SUZUKI] She's never
sounded more beautiful!
[KOKONE] Akira! It's me!
It's really me!
[AKIRA] I can hear you,
loud and clear!
You sound amazing!
Genesis Merge!
[KOKONE]
Reach!
[BOTH]
Aquarion!
[AKIRA, KOKONE]
Sei!
[SAKURAKO]
It looks like a rabbit!
[M.J.B.K. 10A]
Oooto!
[SHOKO] Wow! The sound's
actually visible!
[SAKURAKO] Of course! Her song
and the waves coming off
the M.J.B.K.
cancel each other out!
[SHOKO]
She nullifying its power!
Did you hear that?
Ma'am! I think
sound's coming back!
Kikogami's Verbalism
is expressing itself in song
and overcoming
the M.J.B.K.'s hold!
You're doing it!
"Hanako's voice
calls to us in song!
Behold, sound returns
to the world!
As do mille feuille and
chocolate fondue and macarons!
Praise be to this music!"
[KARAN] "My energy
is back a hundred fold!"
[TSUTOMU] "The kappa has
revived as well! Oh happy day!"
[HAYATO] "Hanako's song
lives among the stars!"
[M.J.B.K. 10A]
Oto! Oto!
[groans]
[KOKONE] A voice without
heart is just noise.
When I was on stage,
my words weren't my own.
I choked.
[AKIRA] The voice is sound
infused with emotion.
It's language.
[KOKONE] And whether
on stage or in life,
if the words tumbling
out of my mouth don't have
real feeling behind them,
my voice doesn't reach anyone.
But when I sing...
I'm truly me!
[AKIRA]
Yes.
--Let your words soar!
--Let my words soar!
[BOTH]
Fill their hearts with song!
[M.J.B.K. 10A]
Oto. Oto...
[groans]
[AKIRA]
It's not over yet.
[KOKONE] Oh no!
We-- We need to g-get back!
[MAIA sighs]
[KARAN]
"I'm all dried up."
"Please. I beg you
to return, Hanako."
"Princess Kaguya,
we must make the necessary
arrangements
so she can return!"
[MAIA]
"Yes. Let us then build
a Baumkuchen castle
together at once."
[SUZUKI, TANAKA]
Mhmm! Mhmm!
[MALE AUDIENCE
MEMBER 10E chuckles]
[MAIA]
Hanako!
♪ Oh, do not fear. ♪
♪ I am back. ♪
♪ I had to search ♪
♪ For my voice. ♪
♪ And now. ♪
♪ At long last, my words come
straight from the heart. ♪
♪ I sing like a bird
set free from her cage! ♪
[AKIRA] "Let us make a
pilgrimage for our salvation!"
[TSUTOMU, MAIA]
Huh?
[AKIRA]
"Onward, friends!"
[CROWD laughs, cheers]
[SAKURAKO] Hey, Akira! You doing
calligraphy all by yourself?
[AKIRA]
Maybe.
[SAKURAKO]
Huh. That's odd.
I thought boys your age
preferred group activities.
[SHOKO] Some boys are team
players, and some are loners.
The Verbalism boys fall
into the latter camp.
[SAKURAKO] Is it possible this
poor young man has no friends?
[SHOKO]
You're just now noticing this?
[SAKURAKO]
Episode Eleven!
[AKIRA]
"Flap! Bound Wings."
I'll be watching it
alone, of course.