Hello.
Thank you folks for
coming all this way
in the middle of a busy weekday.
It's a good thing so
many people out there
have nothing better to do.
[AUDIENCE laughing]
[CHINOSUKE]
Tsutomu.
Hey, I didn't know
if you saw I was here.
'Course I did. Why'd you
sneak out after the show?
Aw, you know, man,
I was just trying not
to steal your thunder.
Your fans'd be all, "Ooh, hey!
Tell us about your younger,
way better looking brother!"
[CHINOSUKE]
Would they now?
[TSUTOMU] Anyway,
I got some stuff to go do.
[CHINOSUKE] Speaking of,
you still doing that thing?
Your... Internet thing?
Online videos?
Oh, yeah, sure am.
[CHINOSUKE] You really are
somethin' special, little bro.
Pursuing the very essence
of comedy for its own sake.
Without a thought
of financial reward.
[HARUKA] I am doubled over
laughing again! Oh, man!
[chuckling]
[CHINOSUKE] You weren't bit
by the comedy bug, you are one.
[SOUGON]
In times past,
humanity was at one
with the world of truth.
But the written word,
for all we prospered from it,
wrought incalculable suffering.
[SAKURAKO] Activation
is still likely possible,
but a Merge is out
of the question.
You should get some rest.
It's a good time for it.
For both the machine and you.
[AKIRA] Fine, a little
R and R, but then, Savior, go.
Please stop calling it that.
[HAYATO]
Commander, can I borrow you?
[SAKURAKO]
Hm?
Swoon!
I can't believe such
a hot young stud
is taking lil' ol' me
out for a drive!
Is this character
you're doing necessary?
[HAYATO] I wanted to speak
with you. About Kaibuki.
[HAYATO] In the battle with the
Flame M.J.B.K. two weeks ago,
without his actions,
we would've been finished.
[SAKURAKO]
That's true.
[HAYATO]
We all know that Kaibuki has
high Verbalism Ability,
but being overly reliant
on a single person
is a sure sign of an
organization's weakness.
At this rate, I worry...
We'll fall apart?
We couldn't do...
I couldn't do anything.
And now something has to change.
[SAKURAKO]
Meow that is a conundwum.
Don't push me.
Don't push me, bro!
Hang on.
I hope no one pushes me in!
Oh, someone just push me alrea--
M-Maia, you p-p-pushed
him too hard!
[KARAN] Tsutomu's about to
be turned into tonkotsu!
Jeez, Tsutomu, no need
to make such a fuss.
If you want some
help, ask nicely.
[SHOKO]
Hey, now!
Drowning on Shirobaco premises
is strictly prohibited.
That new waitress,
Maia's intimidating.
Natural born sadist,
and it's so hot.
So sorry for the wait.
Here's your latte.
[TANAKA screams]
Mr. Customer, sir,
your eyes are all red.
[SUZUKI screams]
Gross, you're eating it?
Yeah, of course we are.
One part boiling soup,
one part scalding bath.
If it worked out how I wanted,
it woulda gone viral in a day.
Want any?
[KOKONE gasping]
[KOKONE]
Th-That touched his lips!
L-Like an in-in-indirect k-kiss!
From Akira. B-B-But
that broth is kind of...
Ts-s-sutomu's, um,
j-juices are, uh...
Does that tube with a hole
in it actually taste good?
[AKIRA] What, you don't
know chikuwa, either?
Want some?
[MAIA, AKIRA]
Awwww.
[KOKONE]
D-Don't!
[AKIRA] I'm sorry. I didn't
realize you wanted it so much.
[KOKONE yelps]
Heh. Someone wants to
eat Akira's meat tube.
[KOKONE]
N-N-N-N-N-No!
That hurts.
[KOKONE]
I-I'm so sorry!
[SUBETE] I can't just
sit on my ass anymore.
I have important
things I need to do.
[NURSE A] Don't run off now,
you pretty young thing.
Aren't you the young heir
to the Nesta fortune?
[SUBETE]
Uhh...
Marrying into money!
For the win!
--[NURSES] Hot stuff! Hot stuff!
--[SUBETE] Whoa! Stop it!
[NURSES]
Hot stuff!
They're like bugs
hunting for husbands.
I'd better be careful then.
Lemme go! Put me down!
I'm already spoken for!
Spare me, please!
[rustling]
[SOUGON]
Hm?
What's wrong?
I'm sorry, it felt
rude to interrupt.
Wouldn't you prefer
to see him in person?
Not interested.
[HAYASHI]
Certainly you noticed.
When they launched last month,
changes to the
operating system
had been made on
all the Vectors.
That last battle
was a risky one,
and could've ended
quite differently.
Had the M.J.B.K. continued
to devour his concept,
Subete's very existence would've
been wiped from this world.
Had that been the case, would
you have resented me forever?
No, I wouldn't blame you.
If he were ended so easily,
he was not meant
for anything greater.
You never change.
[AKIRA]
Grandma, do you feel it?
It feels like we are flying!
"What are you saying... Grandpa?
"We are in the middle
of a bamboo grove."
Kokone, action!
And then, out of nowhere, a huge
peach comes floating along.
It smashes into an iceberg
and starts to sink!
And, cut! Ugh, something
just feels off.
[AKIRA]
Should I be saving the peach?
[TSUTOMU]
Hey!
Huh. Poisoned pineapple
battle royale.
Traveling around the world
inside of a suitcase.
Living for an entire week
surrounded by shaved ice.
What are all these?
Possible gags for my next video.
Which one is best?
I dunno, I feel like
in all of your gags,
it's like you're trying
so hard to be original,
but then there's nothing
new about them at all.
Dang, you sure know how to
stab a guy where it hurts.
Instead of cheap laughs
and reaction videos,
why don't you try some
more elaborate comedy?
Like traditional manzai.
Or storytelling.
[TSUTOMU]
Forget it.
No one understands elaborate
or sophisticated comedy anymore.
They think it's lame
and old fashioned.
Um. Are you okay?
I'm using the modern
medium of the Internet
to try'n find comedy
only I can perform.
Otherwise, there's
just no point.
[AKIRA]
Really, Domon?
Is what you are looking
for... truly comedy?
Is everything all right?
[AKIRA]
A book of gags?
[NEWSCASTER A] In other news, we
visited the Amanuma neighborhood
in the Suginami Ward,
where a very healthy
daikon is growing.
I spoke with the owner
of a small daikon farm,
a man named Hideki,
who recently relocated
from the nearby Nerima Ward
after building a concert venue
over his previous farm
there. Hideki believes...
Not yet. No.
This is not yet "The
World's Best Tempura."
Darling, please, what
has gotten into you?
You haven't slept a
wink since yesterday.
It's like you've turned into
a tempura-making worker bee!
Don't push me!
[NEWSCASTER A]
...radishes larger than average,
with several exceeding
50 or 60 pounds,
but this year, one
of Hideki's daikons
is growing at a rate
he thinks may put it
well over the 100 pound mark.
[HARUKA]
Another amazing video!
Honestly, I doubled
over laughing.
Hello.
I'm commenting because I
happened to see your video.
It was very funny.
I don't think I've ever laughed
that hard before in my life.
Some people may say
unkind things about them,
but I like your videos.
I laugh out loud every time.
But, sometimes,
I wish you'd do stories
or one man plays
like you did at first.
I like your reaction
videos too, though.
[RADIO COMEDIAN]
Whoa. What's this?
There's a bug here on my
pillow I've never seen before.
Looks pretty ugly.
Maybe I oughtta crush
it like the bug it is...
'Scuse me. Check, please?
Thanks, ma'am!
[PROPRIETRESS]
Thank you. Come again!
[TSUTOMU]
The Colic Bug, huh?
[SOUGON]
Verbalize. Rejoice.
Today I deign to set you free!
[M.J.B.K.]
Mushi!
[GUY groaning]
[GUY]
Gotta pass!
[SAKURAKO]
Study bug.
[PROFESSOR]
Research. Research.
I must continue my research.
I must give everything
I have to my research.
[SAKURAKO]
Research bug.
DEAVA System, activate.
[TSUTOMU] Same as it
ever was. Don't they learn?
[HAYATO]
Just keep alert.
[M.J.B.K.]
Mushi.
[KARAN]
Ew.
[SHOKO]
Ugh.
I knew it. It's the
kanji for "insect."
It's big, but size
isn't everything.
Kujyo, Domon,
try using your speed.
Confuse it, then
deal it some damage.
Ten four.
[HAYATO]
Genesis Merge.
[TSUTOMU]
¡Arriba!
[HAYATO, TSUTOMU]
Jin!
[MAIA]
They got eaten whole.
Wh-Wh-Wh-What do we do?
[SHOKO]
Whoa.
I'm still picking up readings
from Aquarion. Could they be?
[TSUTOMU yells]
[TSUTOMU] That coulda gone
better. What is this place?
Belly o' the beast, huh?
You gotta be freakin' kidding.
[SHOKO] Aquarion,
come in. Do you read me?
Shoko, hey.
[SHOKO]
Tsutomu! Are you okay?
Not really sure if
this counts as "okay."
Hayato, thoughts?
Hayato?
Under current government,
economic recovery is
nothing but a dream.
We must heed the call
brothers and sisters.
raise the flag of reform
with the power of youth!
In this current system,
bound up by bureaucracy
and self-interest,
can policies that are truly
for the citizens be established?
[TSUTOMU]
Pull yourself together!
This is bad.
Stuck inside of it like that,
they're suffering the effects
of the M.J.B.K. directly.
H-Hayato's dream is
to be a p-politician.
S-So does that mean...?
What, he's a politics bug?
[HAYATO] Yes, the bureaucratic
system circulates wealth...
But are they both infected?
Tsutomu. You still with us?
Uh, yeah. Seem to be fine.
Commander.
Under the effects
of this M.J.B.K.,
you lose sight of everything
but your dreams and interests.
Like how when you're
obsessed with something,
they say you've "caught a bug."
Yes. What's your point?
[TSUTOMU]
That I'm gonna stay just fine.
[SAKURAKO gasps]
'Cause I'm immune.
I don't have a life
dream or obsession.
Not true! Tsutomu,
you have your comedy.
"Comedy."
Yeah. No. You're wrong.
'Cause the real truth is,
I don't like comedy at all.
[TSUTOMU]
My name is written
with the characters for
"work" and "insect."
Pretty lame, huh?
When I was little, other kids
laughed at it all the time.
Fitting, though.
The joke was on me.
My parents actually thought
they were doing me a favor
when they gave
me this name.
You see, the Domon family
has a pretty storied history.
I come from a long line
of rakugo comedians.
For generations,
our family's produced
masters of the rakugo form.
My older brother,
Chinosuke's the latest.
They've called him
a prodigy for years.
Since I was born into a "comedy
family," as the second son,
a lot of people expected
the same from me.
But Mom and Dad
thought it was cruel
to burden me with
such expectations.
So, to keep there from ever
being any kind of conflict
they gave me a name I could
never be a rakugo comedian with.
My brother is "Chinosuke."
He's "the land."
But all I am is a lowly insect.
A little bug.
Only able to crawl around
on his giant brother's back.
Screw that! No one else
decides how I'll live my life!
Who gives a damn about
the traditional arts?
I'm sick of all of it!
And it's not for me.
All I want is to break out
of those crusty old traditions.
To forge my own path
with my own comedy.
Are those eggs?
Those baby M.J.B.K.'s
cannot hatch.
If they do, I'm worried
they'll start eating words.
[SHOKO]
But if that happens,
the word corrosion rate
will increase dramatically.
[HARUKA] That was so funny.
I doubled over laughing.
I loved it. I was
laughing out loud.
Is that...?
[HARUKA]
Tsutomu's hysterical.
Haruka?
[HARUKA laughing]
Tsutomu has a fan?
Guess she must've caught
the Tsutomu bug.
Can you hear that,
Domon? That laughter?
You can be as hard
on yourself as you like,
but someone out there
loves your comedy.
She's moved by it.
Hearing this voice. Does it
make you feel anything?
[TSUTOMU]
No, I...
The truth is. I...
That's Tsutomu's
private property.
[KOKONE]
Wha-- A-Akira?
As such, the youth who are
concentrated in cities...
[TSUTOMU] To paraphrase a wise
man: Life moves pretty fast.
if you don't stop and face
your fears once in a while,
you could miss it.
[TSUTOMU]
Hello, fine folks.
Lemme sit right down and
tell you a truly trivial tale.
I woke up one morning
just in time to see a little bug
crawl up onto my pillow.
You're a]disgusting
little thing!
I must destroy you!
And when I lifted my hand back
up, I heard this tiny voice.
Please, spare me!
Oh my! A bug that can talk?
Yes, good sir...
What is that he's doing?
It's rakugo.
[TSUTOMU] Holy Roly Poly,
you really can speak!
I have definitely never
seen that before.
"Colic Bug," huh?
I feel like I've heard of that.
Hm. Are you a good bug or bad?
[SAKURAKO]
Of course.
This M.J.B.K. is making itself
grow by literally eating kanji.
But if all of that
kanji it's consuming
were to suddenly start conveying
different meanings than usual.
You mean, if these obsession
bugs, or whatever they are,
were to somehow
lose their focus,
it would most likely affect
the M.J.B.K., too?
[KARAN]
Uh.
Ha! We need to make
the bug kanji laugh!
[KOKONE]
B... B-B-B...
But... The b-bug's voice is
too loud. Th-They can't hear!
[AKIRA]
No problem.
For I am, the savior of comedy.
I dunno, sir,
he just told us to hook
loudspeakers up to his Vector,
so we jerry-rigged one
of the base's big ones.
What? The order didn't come
down from the commander?
Wait a minnit, Colic Bug?
You mean like a
stomach bug! You pain!
You make me sick! Literally!
I must destroy you!
[M.J.B.K.]
Mushi!
[TSUTOMU]
Please! Spare me!
If you let me live, I'll tell
you our secret weakness!
Your secret weakness?
By all means: speak up.
Well, it's kind of
embarrassing, but...
...we hate red peppers.
When we're in a
person's stomach
and they send red
peppers our way,
we've gotta hustle down south...
[AKIRA]
Speaker: On!
[TSUTOMU]
Your other home?
Think of it like a
summer rental. Real nice!
It's on that little "peninsula"
dangling between a man's legs.
[KOKONE]
Wha-- W-W-Wha--?
Am I too young for this?
"The Colic Bug." Classic rakugo.
[TSUTOMU]
"Peninsula?"
More like, "pe-nis-ula!"
That's valuable real estate!
Do you all hear that?
The kanji are laughing.
Oh, man!
Hayato, what's wrong?
What a ridiculous story.
[TSUTOMU]
Okay, fine,
so on men you've got another
dangly little safehouse.
How 'bout when it's a lady?
Oh, well. In that case,
we've got nowhere to run.
Aquarion's being washed
away in the monster's bile.
So the bug's trying to
expel them from its body.
In other words, the bug
is debugging itself.
[TSUTOMU] All right, now here
comes the punch line.
You ready, Hayato?
Ready! Genesis Merge.
[TSUTOMU]
Pierce it!
[BOTH]
Aquarion!
[TSUTOMU, HAYATO]
Ryu!
[AKIRA]
The kanji for "insect"
came from a variation
of the one for "dragon."
[TSUTOMU] You've been
layin' eggs all over.
Which means we know
you're female.
Ladies don't have another house.
A woman's womb,
we gotta pierce through that
on our way to a new future!
[BOTH]
Go, Tsutomu!
Pierce it!
[AKIRA]
Do it! Be a dragon!
A dragon that
pierces the heavens!
[TSUTOMU]
Pierce it!
And the dragon,
born of her womb,
rose to the heavens
as a rainbow!
[M.J.B.K.]
Mushi! Mushi! Mushi!
[TSUTOMU] Not sure when or
how it all got turned around.
But you know? I really
did want to love comedy.
[TSUTOMU]
I wanted to learn to love it.
I just wasn't ready
to recognize that yet.
[TSUTOMU]
But, from here on,
I'm gonna try my
best to face it.
You're the one who made
me realize that, Haruka.
Let me show you my thanks.
Aw, man. Palms are sweating.
[HARUKA]
Are you Tsutomu?
Yes!
[yelps]
My, quite a looker in person.
You... must be...
Miss... Haruka?
Yes. That's me. I'm Haruka.
[HARUKA]
Oh, dear.
[chuckles] Ba-dum-bum,
ba-dum-bum.
[SHOKO]
Oh, hey, Maia.
Have you ever played
hide and seek?
[MAIA]
Never heard of it.
[SHOKO] Holy cats, I knew
you were kinda sheltered,
but did you grow up
under a rock, or what?
[MAIA]
What?
Why would I need to be
placed under a rock?
Do you mean to
imprison me again?
[SHOKO]
Huh?
[AKIRA]
No worries.
I won't let anyone
lock you away.
For I am--
[SHOKO] Yes, yes, we know!
Next time, Episode 9.
[MAIA] "Clear Them!
The Inviting Shadows."