[SOUGON]
Script.
A means of communication
for sharing thought,
relaying raw information.
[SOUGON] Of all the
world's writing systems,
one is utterly unique. Special.
[SOUGON]
Kanji.
Verbalize.
[SOUGON] Unlike hiragana
or the Arabic alphabet,
kanji conveys two
things in and of itself.
Sound and meaning.
Utterance, significance.
Its relationship to these gives
the ancient script
enormous hidden power.
[SOUGON] Concrete thing
or abstract image.
The human mind cannot help
but substitute the
word for the reality.
If the word for something
were to be destroyed.
The very concept it
represents would disappear.
Reality would shift.
Modern civilization would
fall to ruin on the instant.
[SOUGON]
In times past,
humanity was at one
with the world of truth,
but the written word,
for all we prospered from it,
wrought incalculable suffering.
[SHOKO] Come on!
You're the manager do something!
[SUZUKI] What are you
waiting for? Call Kokone!
[TANAKA] Without the
Verbalism Reading Corner,
Shirobaco is just a café.
[OURA]
Ugh. Is Hayato still not here?
[SHOKO sighs]
[SAKURAKO] This isn't looking
good where is everybody?
Cut me some slack,
people you should be here.
We should've kicked
things off ten minutes ago.
[ITOU]
I see the hype isn't unfounded.
The ladies do adore you.
I don't know about that, sir.
Says "Hayato Kujyo of
the Piercing Good Looks."
[HATANO] You ought'a
see the pile of fanmail
he rakes in every month.
I'm the Diet member,
and all they care
about is my secretary.
S'enough to give
a guy a complex.
[ITOU] Now, now. None of us does
our civic duty for the fame.
[TSUTOMU] Seriously.
Fate brought us together.
I can feel it.
That's the only explanation.
Call it "Destiny in Asagaya."
'S got a ring, right?
[GIRL 1A laughs]
Yeah, no.
[GIRL 1B] Seriously.
This place is a joke.
[TSUTOMU] Aw, c'mon
don't be that way.
[TSUTOMU] Shibuya and
Shinjuku are so predictable.
Think about it:
They're tourist traps.
Meeting the love of your life in
Asagaya? You don't expect that.
It's a surprise. It's special.
Right? Ya don't see sump'm
comin', it stays with ya.
[GIRL 1B] So you gonna
answer your phone, or what?
Eh, let it ring.
Probably just the
imminent doom
of the human race or something.
No bigs.
Who's got the energy to
worry about that stuff
when the here and
now is where it's at?
No time like the present!
I appreciate this, but surely
you've got better things to do?
I am capable of
taking care of myself.
Nuh no, it's fuh-fine, ma'am.
More than happy to help.
These bags are t-too
heavy for one person.
Aren't you a dear.
Don't m-mention it.
You're just headed to
the, buh, to the b-bu?
[KOKONE] "You're on the
way to bus station, right?
Don't worry it's okay.
My boss won't mind
if I'm a little bit late."
[OLD LADY 1A]
Really? Well, if you're sure.
[KOKONE]
Help!
[AKIRA]
She your grandmother?
Oh.
[KOKONE]
Th-Th-Thank you.
I was nearby and
heard your voice.
When there's a cry for help,
I come running ready to lend
a hand wherever there's a need.
I have to...
...because I am The Savior.
It was certainly
nice of him to help,
but maybe the poor young man's
spent a little too much time
in the sun.
Huh?
Hmm.
Now is the time for rejoicing.
For today I deign
to set you free!
[eerie wailing]
[M.J.B.K. TWIST]
Maaaaaakiiii!
--Huh?
--[GIRL STUDENT 1C] What is it?
[GIRL STUDENT 1B]
Something wrong?
[SOUGON] Injected
with the Nesta Virus,
the afflicted kanji will
writhe to life, become bestial.
What happens next
is enthralling.
[MALE SUSHI CHEF 1A]
Huh? What the?
[HAYATO]
I'm very sorry, but..
...if you'll please excuse me.
[HATANO] Hey!
Kujyo, where're you going?
[SOUGON] That which in the
mundane world corresponds
to the character
reacts violently.
Somebody help me!
[SOUGON]
The concept runs amok,
like a wild animal
freed from its tether.
Unbelievable, right?
[GIRL 1B laughs]
It doesn't have any twists!
That's hilarious!
What's up with
all that noise?
--[HAYATO] Hey! Look out!
--[TSUTOMU] Heads up!
He could've
flattened us. Idiot!
[HAYATO]
Are you guys okay?
[TSUTOMU]
Hayato?
Tsutomu? What're you...?
[BOY 1A] Doesn't
that belong to Kokone?
To whom?
[BOY 1A] Seriously?
Kokone of Shiroboco!
[AKIRA]
So that was real.
This is handmade.
She'll want it back.
[distant sirens]
[OLD LADY 1A sighs] I spoil
my grandchildren terribly.
Thank you so much, sweetheart,
I don't know what
possessed me to think
I could carry all
these toys by myself.
Good thing you insisted.
Oh, uh, I...
--Huh?
[sirens]
[people screaming]
[OLD LADY 1A]
Augh!
[KOKONE]
Get down!
A twister? Then this must be...
[MAN grunting]
[SHOKO] Hold still, will ya?
I'll try'n cut it loose.
This is really happening.
Man, this M.J.B.K.
Clumsy piece of work.
[MAIA] We've had this
discussion, Subete.
No eating in the cockpit.
[SUBETE]
Right. Sorry, Maia.
At long last
the time has come.
I shall fulfill the mission
and meet my destiny.
[WOMAN 1A grunts]
Get this off of me.
[AKIRA]
Hey!
It's y-you.
[AKIRA]
Perfect timing.
[KOKONE] I'm s-sorry,
I uh, I can't talk right now.
I have to go!
Hang on a sec.
No! Let go of me!
There's no time!
The world is...
I mean, it's in... I have to go!
[KOKONE gasps]
S-Sorry I'm late!
[TSUTOMU] Nice of you
to join us, Kokone.
[SAKURAKO]
Attention please.
The café is closed
until further notice.
Sorry for the inconvenience.
[KENTO]
Thanks for droppin' by.
We'll see you again real soon.
[KENTO]
Help you?
[HAYATO]
Manager?
[SAKURAKO] You may
dispense with that title.
[SAKURAKO]
From this point forward,
you will address me
as "Commander."
DEAVA System, activate!
--[MALE B] Right.
--[FEMALE A] We're online.
--[MALE B] All systems go.
--[FEMALE A] Vector machines.
--[FEMALE A] Standby for launch.
--[MALE A] Launch platforms...
...at the ready.
[SAKURAKO] Formation: Delta.
Kujyo and Domon, you're up.
Get in there.
[HAYATO]
Roger.
[TSUTOMU]
On it.
So you're sending
us out for real?
Not to be "that guy,"
but you know I've never actually
been in one of these before.
[SAKURAKO]
You'll be fine.
This is what you've
been training for.
Every moment spent honing
your skills has led to this.
Remember: it's not technique or
intellect that moves a vector.
It's Verbalism Ability.
Use your voice.
Speak from the heart,
and the vector will respond.
[SHOKO] Vector exit lane
link system: operational.
[SHOKO]
Connection complete.
Verbalize.
Welp, you only
live once. Verbalize!
[FEMALE STATION ANNOUNCER 1A]
Underground Water Storage Valve
open. Water catchment
tanks filling up.
All pathways around
the station will be sealed.
Activating mirage field now.
[SHOKO] Mirage field complete.
Image is locked down.
Vectors launch!
[M.J.B.K. TWIST]
Maki!
That's our guy.
I hope Tsutomu
and Hayato are ready.
Do not falter.
[AKIRA] Oh. So that's what
everyone's panicking about?
[SHOKO]
Who the...?
[KOKONE]
You fuh followed me?
[SAKURAKO]
How did you get in here?
Where's Kento?
[KOKONE] No! W-W-Wait.
He's not dangerous!
[SAKURAKO] Kikogami.
Do you know this guy?
[KOKONE]
Well, I... I...
[AKIRA]
Put me up there.
[AKIRA] That thing's a
threat to the world, right?
Let me destroy it for you.
Put me in one of those machines.
I do not take orders from...
[AKIRA] With this hand,
I will save the world.
For I am The Savior.
What a cheese ball.
[SAKURAKO]
This isn't a game, son,
and I don't have
time to indulge you.
Get him out of here!
--[MALE SECURITY 1A] Ma'am.
--[MALE SECURITY 1B] Roger that.
[MALE SECURITY 1A]
Move it, kid.
[MALE SECURITY 1B]
No funny stuff.
[TSUTOMU]
This isn't working!
[M.J.B.K. TWIST]
Maki!
You have Verbalism!
That's supposed
to be the only power
that'll take the M.J.B.K. down!
Tsutomu! It's time to Merge!
No offense, man,
but I was kinda hoping my
first time would be with Kokone.
Aw, what the hell.
'S better than dying!
[HAYATO]
Let's do this!
What's happening?
What's the big fuss?
All we have to do is guard him.
Conditions for victory
couldn't be better!
Don't start getting
careless on me.
Yeah, yeah.
Whatever. I know.
Our duty is to Master
Sougon's sublime ideal.
eliminating all who interfere.
[SUBETE]
Absolutely. Well said, Maia.
Is this what the Commander
was talking about?
I suppose a degree of
resistance is to be expected.
Sakurako Soda, I presume?
If memory serves,
you stole my vector machines.
I advise all haste, madam.
Your precious words
are poised to vanish utterly.
Puh-Please, ma'am!
Send me up!
Go time.
[KOKONE]
Ah! W-Wait! That's m-my vector.
[TSUTOMU]
Aw, crap!
Another one!
Kikogami?
[AKIRA] I'm sorry.
You're a threat to this world.
He shouldn't be able to...!
How can this
guy pilot a vector?
[SAKURAKO] He must
have Verbalism Ability.
Even so, how can
he man the controls
without a suit or
the necessary training?
[SHOKO]
No data from Vector One.
He's gone off the grid.
[SAKURAKO] Retrieve Kujyo's and
Domon's vectors. immediately!
[SHOKO]
Yes, ma'am!
[SUBETE] Yeah, I'd say
that's game, set, and match.
[MAIA] I shall be able to
fulfill the mission very soon.
At last my reason
for living will bear fruit.
Your orders, ma'am?
I'm afraid we're completely
out of working craft!
[M.J.B.K. TWIST]
Maki!
[FEMALE OPERATOR 1A]
The Shuto Highway and all
major thoroughfares in the area
have been closed to traffic.
No fatalities reported as yet.
[FEMALE OPERATOR 1B] ...the
mysterious cloud formations
seen over the downtown area...
Ma'am! Look at this!
[AKIRA] No. I won't let
it end. I made a decision.
It's my job to protect
the world. I am The Savior.
[AKIRA]
With this hand...
...I will save.
Uh, do you see what I see?
"The voice infused with
spirit bestows power
and meaning upon our words."
Maybe this is what the
true nature of Verbalism
is really all about.
Come.
[AKIRA]
Come!
[MAIA]
Wha... What is this?
Maia, no!
What's going on? The controls!
Genesis Merge!
[MAIA]
My voice!
Now shout!
--Aquarion!
[AKIRA]
This is it.
I've been waiting
for this moment.
[MAIA]
What's happening to me?
I've done this
countless time before,
but it's never felt like this.
This is wonderful!
--[MAIA] Kou!
--[AKIRA] Kou!
[SUBETE]
What's going on? Maia!
[MAIA]
I can feel it.
You're Akira Kaibuki.
[AKIRA]
That's right.
And you're Maia Tsukigane.
I know what I have to do.
I was born for this.
Who the hell are you?
[M.J.B.K. TWIST]
Maki!
[SAKURAKO]
Incredible. Who are these two?
[M.J.B.K. TWIST]
Maki!
[AKIRA]
Let's go.
--[AKIRA] Mugen Punch!
--[MAIA] Mugen Punch!
[M.J.B.K. TWIST]
Maki! Urgg!
--[MAIA] Go!
--[AKIRA] Go!
What the hell are
you supposed to be?
I am The Savior.
[KOKONE] So, thi-this
is the Preview Corner.
[MAIA]
Hey!
Where do you get off
appearing out of nowhere?
That's right,
I'm talkin' to you!
[AKIRA] When there's a
threat looming over the world.
[MAIA]
Don't start!
[KOKONE]
Excuse me, b-b-but, uh...
[MAIA] I can't believe
you pulled a Merge on me!
You dare defy Master Sougon?
I'm The Savior. Duh.
Will you stop saying that?
S-Sorry, all out of time.
N-Next episode...
[AKIRA]
"Shine! Light of Thought."
[MAIA]
Shut up!