[TSUTOMU]
'Sup!
Salutations to all you dudes
and dudettes out there.
I'm your handsome host with
the most, Tstutomu Domon.
Today, I'm showin' you the
hazards of choppin' up an onion!
Cover for me.
All right. See you
later, I guess.
[AKIRA]
Are you going to Nesta again?
Where I go is my business.
[KARAN screams]
Why is it so hard
to remember them?
Just try to focus.
Learning the inherent
subtleties of kanji is vital.
Otherwise, you'll grow
up to be like him.
If that's true, I'm gonna
study until my eyes bleed.
[KOKONE] Here, Tsutomu.
I brought tissues.
[TSUTOMU, KOKONE sneezing]
Then again, I won't worry
'bout growin' up just yet.
[SAKURAKO]
Pssst, Karan.
Quiet on the set please.
Like, gag me with a spoon!
Gag you... with a spoon?
Did she just Valley
Girl? Is it the 80s?
Like, wicked bogus.
That's old, too!
[SUZUKI]
Hey, what's this?
And now, suburban strangeness,
where massive vines are growing.
[KARAN]
Let me see.
[SUZUKI]
Oh, sure.
[NEWSCASTER]
According to the homeowner,
the plant growth just
appeared out of nowhere.
The sheer speed of their
surge is unnatural.
[SD MAKI]
Maki!
[BOTH gasp]
[KARAN]
You guys, look at this!
Karan!
[HAYATO]
Show us.
[KOKONE]
What is it?
[TSUTOMU] No way's that
news chick funnier'n me!
[KARAN] Not her,
knucklehead! Look closer!
[TSUTOM gasps]
[KOKONE]
Why is there an M.J.B.K?
[SHOKO]
What? An M.J.B.K? Where?
[HAYATO]
You can't see it?
[SHOKO]
See what? A news interview?
[TSUTOMU]
No, he's right there!
[SUZUKI] Come on, you
guys, that's my phone.
It sprung up overnight?
Yes. I planted some peppers
here, but they all died.
It seems regular
people can't see it.
I could've sworn we
iced that one already!
[SUZUKI]
Can I please have my phone back?
[SOUGON]
In times past,
humanity was at one
with the world of truth.
but the written word,
for all we prospered from it,
wrought incalculable suffering.
Somebody's got a
case of the Mondays!
I've had it worse, so I'm
gonna keep on truckin'!
[SAKURAKO] According to incoming
reports from across all sectors,
the usage of words and phrases
that have gone out of favor
is on the rise.
Naturally, the M.J.B.K. is
assumed to be responsible.
[BOTH]
Radi-cool, home slice!
Where's the beef?
Right. Here.
'Cause baby got back!
[BOTH] Did it. Said it.
Stole my momma's credit!
"Night of the
Living Dead" cliché.
Words rising from the grave.
We sent the Vectors
out for reconnaissance.
They found the kanji for "death"
scattered throughout
the Logos World.
However...
No M.J.B.K. There's nothing.
[SAKURAKO]
This could very well be
a unique characteristic
of the death kanji.
Death is devoid of life.
Therefore, the M.J.B.K.
for death doesn't exist.
So instead, it's distorting
the very concept of death,
and reviving M.J.B.K.s.
Why're they able to cross into
our world all of a sudden?
Like, how's that even work?
[KENTO] Ever since the battle
with the Nothingness M.J.B.K.,
what DEAVA calls the Logos
World, or Wordspace,
has been incredibly unstable.
Like what happened
the other day.
You're right,
their appearance in our world
could be much like Hito's.
A unique problem
we've attributed
to the erosion of the boundaries
between our two worlds.
The M.J.B.K.s that have
appeared are much weaker,
and normal people
without Verbalism Ability
can't even see them.
So the situation remains
relatively calm, for now.
However, given the existence
of a death M.J.B.K.,
we'll have to subdue these newly
revived ones to end the chaos.
[TSUTOMU] Question.
You said "subdue them."
You talkin' 'bout like,
a net, or a lasso, or--?
Nope, sorry. They can
only be stopped.
"By an Aquarion."
Well, that doesn't help
us because technically,
Aquarion shouldn't be able
to Merge in our world.
I say we throw our hands up in
desperation and go take a nap.
That's adorable, but no.
We can't save the
world by napping.
[SAKURAKO]
I have a plan.
If we can't beat
them in our world,
we'll have to send them back
to where M.J.B.K.s come from.
You said that like
it's a possibilty.
[SAKURAKO]
Yes!
And so, when something strange
appears in our neighborhood,
who you gonna call?
The special task force I just
threw together! Codename:
Asagaya Yurei Busters!
♪ Yurei Busters. ♪
The Asagaya Yurei
Busters? How original!
This task force consists of you.
[MAIA squealing]
But I thought we were
already the Verbalism Club.
My copyright infringement
sense is tingling.
[SAKURAKO]
I was afraid something like this
might happen, so I had uniforms
made weeks ago. Get changed.
How are these jumpsuits
supposed to help?
They don't.
They're grey, and
dumb, and not cute.
Bustin' makes me feel good.
Your vacuum rig is pretty neat.
[HAYATO growls]
♪ Yurei Busters! ♪
Roll out, Asagaya Yurei Busters,
and show these M.J.B.K.s
how we do things downtown!
[TSUTOMU] So are you
the mayor or the EPA guy?
It looks like the manager's
really cheered back up.
--She's forcing it.
--[KOKONE] ♪ Yurei Busters! ♪
[BAKER]
This may be my masterpiece.
This roll pan is twisted.
You can make a sandwich
from a sand worm.
[MAIA] You seem to be
having some trouble.
Who're you?
[AKIRA] We are the task force
assembled to save the world.
The Asagaya Yurei Busters!
[beeping]
Got a signal. Over there.
I'm just a baker, man!
Found it!
[MAIA]
Judgment time has come!
Go, Aquaripen!
Now, draw!
[SAKURAKO] It's a prototype
developed by the technicians
at DEAVA: The Aquaripen.
With this, attuned users can
channel Verbalism Ability
to some degree in the
real world. In theory.
Straighten up this mess! Direct!
[SD MAKI]
M-M-M-Maki!
[TSUTOMU]
Snap! It freakin' vanished!
[HAYATO] It is possible
to damage an M.J.B.K.
simply by manifesting
an appropriate word.
That attack should've sent
it to the death dimension.
[KOKONE] Hey, Maia,
tha-that was really cool!
[HAYATO] We've defeated
13 of them so far,
which means there
are a dozen left.
And all the M.J.B.K.s
have gathered in Asagaya.
Why're the little
dudes coming here?
I can't be certain,
but many of our greatest writers
have called Asagaya home
at pivotal points
in their careers.
Perhaps, from beyond the grave,
the souls of those
literary giants beckon
and draw the
M.J.B.K.s ever closer.
[KARAN]
Who cares?
Let's just fix all this
weird nostalgia stuff.
before it gets any worse.
None of these are
fond memories for me.
I'm not even old enough
to get these references.
[YOKO] What? As if!
He's not my boyfriend.
He's just my wheels, you follow?
[MIHO] I want to bag a rich
one and be a kept woman!
Fix this weird nostalgia?
You sure that's what
they said, homes?
[YUJI] Yeah, man! That's
totally what they said!
[KARAN]
Wait!
--[SD MUSHI] Mushi!
--[SD NATSU] Natsu.
[SD MUSHI]
Mushi. Mushi. Mushi. Mushi.
[TAKASHI]
Hold on.
[AKIRA]
Hm?
Oh no! The bug's getting away!
We won't let you change
things. Retro is rad.
To the max!
Who're you people
supposed to be?
[TSUTOMU grumbles]
I don't know who you cats are,
or what you're after, you dig?
But if you jive turkeys
wanna put the kibosh
on our mega-cool vibe,
I will not sit back and let
you kill these anachronisms!
We're psychedelic!
Just wait til we
strap on our keytars.
How old are you? You guys
should so know better.
That was awkward.
[YUJI]
What was that, punk?
Don't make me fling
a laserdisc at'cha!
How sad.
Along with the outdated lingo,
they've reverted to
feelings and attitudes
from when they were younger.
Truly unfortunate.
[YOKO] What's your
problem, soy sauce face?
Just 'cause you're square
doesn't mean we're not trendy.
[MIHO]
Respecting your elders
should be as natural as
an Atari Maeda Cracker.
That's so sad.
What're they even saying?
What's goin' on with these
horribly lame people?
They're M.K. Fives.
Huh? What does that mean?
She's ready to murder or
kill them in five seconds.
Well that's extreme!
[alarm blaring]
[SAKURAKO]
What's up?
Bad news. Word corrosion is
rising! This doesn't look good!
Something's here.
[TAKASHI whimpers]
[ALL gasp]
Where'd my dead
grandpa come from?
But, Dad, you died in a car
accident three years ago.
Mega lame!
[HAYATO]
This is...
Death. And it's come to
try to change our world.
[SHOKO] Looks like the dead
kanji in the Logos World
are finished.
They should all
disintegrate soon enough.
[beeping]
[SHOKO]
But even so,
the word corrosion rate
is still on the rise!
There are signs of it
cropping up everywhere!
[MAN A]
Mom?
Mother, why're you here?
I missed you!
[MAN A screams]
[thud]
[MAN B]
Hey!
[SAKURAKO] Well this is
a disturbing wrinkle.
The living are being
harassed by the dead.
We're talking total buzzkill.
You're too noisy, Commander.
That was mean! Meanie.
[SD MUSHI]
Mushi. Bug. Mushi. Wind.
It's down.
We're not done yet.
There're a bunch of
'em floating around.
[MAIA]
And more of 'em every second.
[beeping]
[SHOKO] At this rate, the
boundary between life and death
will become increasingly
vague as time goes on
until there are a dozen dead
for every living person.
Like cats and dogs
living together,
we're talking mass hysteria!
Let's go. Someone's
got to end this.
You're right.
It's time for the Yurei
Busters to make a move.
[SHOKO]
Um, Kento? What're you doing?
Well, I just realized
if we try to deal with
the M.J.B.K.s one by one,
it'll take far too long,
so I'll see if I can
find a kanji that lets us
take the fight to the death
M.J.B.K. more directly.
Normally, we rely on Aquarion
and the kids' Verbalism Ability.
This time, I can help.
Good call. I'll
take a look, too.
[TSUTOMU screaming]
What was that?
[SD YUME]
Yume. Yume.
[TSUTOMU]
That thing's freaky lookin'!
[SD YUME]
Yume? Yume.
What's the deal? Dream Machine
is like, three stories tall.
I wish I knew.
--No clue on this end.
--Yeah, I don't know either.
[MR. KIHACHI]
Okay, gather round!
Each one of you young
bucks listen up!
You're not past your prime.
I see potential in you! No joke!
But you gotta want it!
It's never too late to start!
Got it? Believe and
dreams come true!
[BASEBALL PLAYER A]
Never give up on your dreams!
[BASEBALL PLAYER B] In my
dreams, I don't have bursitis!
[BASEBALL PLAYERS
laughing, cheering]
I'll just try to erase it.
I don't really think that's
gonna work on these guys.
But you never know until
you try. Right, Hayato?
Poor fools.
Their hearts have been
ensnared by dreams,
undoubtedly benefiting
the M.J.B.K.
Which leaves us
only one thing to do.
[TSUTOMU]
I smell a plan brewin'.
[KARAN]
Uhh, Big Bro?
You heard right!
Dreams have the power to
make us all better people!
I had to tell you guys
because you all deserve it!
I just knew you guys...
...you guys would... get it!
[MR. KIHACHI crying]
Give it a rest. These dreams
have zero chance of coming true.
[MR. KIHACHI gasps]
What are you saying, you idiot?
Don't give up! That's the
only way dreams come true!
I have three questions.
Huh? Sure, go ahead.
How many of you guys played
on little league teams
when you were children?
And as those children,
how many of you dreamed
of one day going pro?
Now, show of hands.
Did that come true?
[HAYATO] It's delusional to
think your dreams will come true
if you just believe
strongly enough.
It's not that dreams
don't come true
because people give up on them.
People have to set
aside their dreams
because they won't come true.
Hard work alone
isn't everything.
Do you think the best
pitcher in the world
is the guy who put in
the most hard work?
The guy who practiced
the hardest?
That's seldom the case at all!
Every person has their
own special traits
where you can and can't go
is delineated by talent.
Yet you... you promise
their dreams will come true
if they simply
work hard enough.
That mistaken teaching only
gives people false hope.
And ultimately,
brings them misfortune.
Listen, most dreams
never come true.
More often than not, all your
misplaced work goes to waste.
And now, you're chasing after
yours this late in the game?
You'd be crazy to expect
positive results.
Go home to your families,
your wives, your kids.
If you're that fortunate,
stop wasting time here
on impossible dreams.
Instead go take care
of the ones you love.
And be sure to teach
your children this:
"You were born to
an unimpressive,
ordinary dope like me!
So the odds are pretty low
you'll ever have the talent
to be someone great!
But still,
you must live your life as fully
as your limitations allow!"
[MR. KIHACHI] Did you have
to be so unbelievably brutal?
Guys, now's your chance!
[KOKONE, KARAN, TSUTOMU]
Huh?
Don't "huh?" me! The M.J.B.K.
has been weakened!
[KOKONE, KARAN, TSUTOMU]
Oh.
People's dreams are fleeting.
Wow, that's real sad.
[SD YUME]
Yume.
Job done. But um, ya know?
[KARAN]
Totally fiendish, Big Bro.
[TSUTOMU]
Fiend man.
[KOKONE]
Demon!
[HAYATO]
You want me to cry too?
[AKIRA]
This way! I saw one!
[MAIA]
Ugh! Crap!
Hold it! No!
Um? You guys again?
You're not getting past us, dig?
How 'bout them apples?
[ALL laughing]
Pick a decade.
Do you even understand
what's happening here?
[AKIRA] If the boundary between
life and death vanishes,
the damage will be severe.
This is a threat to the world.
So if you keep insisting
on aiding its progress,
I won't have mercy.
[gasps]
Akira.
Wha--? Chill out! No need
to get all serious here, man!
Yeah!
That kinda attitude's never
really been in style, baby.
Look, relax, kid!
What's wrong with our choices?
We're rediscovering
lost passions, buddy!
Like we're getting a second
shot at being young!
If having fun is wrong,
I don't wanna be right!
Ya got that, bozo?
Wha--?
Master... Sougon?
[TSUTOMU growls] Get back here!
Ugh! Lost sight of it.
Yo, Hayato, what's up?
Go on ahead without me.
[TSUTOMU grunts]
Hello, Dad.
You came back.
[TAKASHI] Everybody's happy!
What's so wrong with that?
You got an answer, bub?
Please, step aside.
[TAKASHI]
Huh?
Those kids are
trying to get by you.
Uh, wait, what kids?
They are?
[KOKONE] The M.J.B.K. sh-should
be around here somewhere.
[music playing]
What a racket!
It is a b-bit loud.
[KARAN]
What the heck is this?
[KOKONE]
Umm. Para Para?
We can't get by them.
But I wanted to play.
They've blocked those kids.
[KARAN grumbling]
Right! That does it!
[AKIRA]
Tell me.
Do you know why words
and phrases die out?
There's a time in life when
people shine their brightest.
Those trendy words are tied
directly to when we're young.
[pop]
Hey, who killed the tunes?
What's goin' on? Crank it up!
Have some common courtesy!
[KARAN yelling]
[AKIRA] You can't monopolize
that time to shine.
Eventually, it has to pass
on to the next generation.
We're still so young.
We haven't made enough memories
to be nostalgic about!
But now? This is our time!
It's our time right here!
I wanna grow up! But please,
let me enjoy my childhood first!
The future never waits.
Make the most of your time.
That's why death exists.
For words and for people.
Please don't come
back now, Father.
I love you, but I've learned
to stand on my own two feet.
[HAYATO] Though I inherited
your lack of talent,
that's been a struggle.
You good now, bro?
Yeah. I'll be all right.
You came because you
were worried about me.
I'm sorry for being such a
high maintenance old lady.
I'm ready now to
make your grave.
[KENTO gasps]
[KENTO] I found it!
This one should work!
[SHOKO]
I've just sent you guys a map.
All members of the
Asagaya Yurei Busters,
gather at the designated
location at once.
And when you get there,
you'll materialize kanji
by working together!
[KARAN gasps]
But I'm still learning my
kanji! I'm not very good.
[KOKONE]
Here.
If you need help, ask,
like a grown up.
[BOY B chuckling]
[BOY B]
Trick or treat!
Here, kid, wear
this if you want.
[TAKASHI chuckles]
[TAKASHI] It looks good
on you, chief! Have fun!
[BOYS]
Thanks, mister!
[AKIRA]
Maia, I will save the world.
Yeah. I know that.
[AKIRA] I am the Savior.
The one who'll save the world.
And if you're ever lonely...
...I'll save you too.
[SHOKO]
Report in. Is everyone ready?
I'm good to go whenever.
Yeah, I'm r-ready!
I'm as ready as I'm gonna be.
These things are toast!
Then let's light 'em up!
O dead words and drifting souls!
Rest in peace beneath the earth!
[GROUP]
Burial!
Till we meet again.
--Why am I dressed like this?
--Why are we wearing this?
--It's cold!
--We're not 20 anymore!
Guess I'll see you at
the office tomorrow.
Back to the grindstone.
[SHOKO] Now we just have to
eradicate the mini M.J.B.K.s
that we sent over
to the other side.
Project.
[SHOKO] Why'd the monitor
turn on by itself?
[SAKURAKO]
The M.J.B.K.s have reverted
to their original sizes?
[SUBETE]
Sit down and watch.
Who?
[SUBETE] O pitiful souls
of the departed...
[SUBETE]
...let all of you be reduced...
...to pure light.
With one strike.
[SHOKO]
No. It can't be!
[MAIA]
Akira.
[SD MAKI]
What's an excavation, Maki?
[SD YUME] It means digging
up old stuff, Yume.
[SD MUSHI]
No, Mushi. The dig site is.
[SD UZU]
In a foreign desert, whirl!
[SD MU]
It's hot, Mu.
[SD NATSU] They don't speak
our language there, Natsu.
[SD MAKI]
Maki!
[SD YUME] You can't
watch Logos there, Yume!
[SD MUSHI]
Episode 16.
[SD NATSU] "Carve Them In!
The Scars of Destiny."
[MAIA]
I'm scared.