[CHILD SUBETE] We were
supposed to be together.
Remember? I made a promise.
[SUBETE]
Why? Why?!
[AKIRA]
Combine.
[groans]
[SUBETE groans]
[groans, pants]
[SUBETE]
No.
Damn it.
Why can't I beat you?
[SOUGON] In times past,
humanity was at one
with the world of truth.
But the written word,
for all we prospered from it,
wrought incalculable suffering.
I can't do it.
This is far too painful.
If this is what
it means to be alive,
the world can't disappear
soon enough.
This is fate. I'll happily
embrace nothingness.
Is something wrong?
It's coming.
[SHOKO] Heads up.
Registering a new M.J.B.K.!
What are you talking about?
[SOUGON] The Great Word
reacted to Subete's aura
and assumed a different
form accordingly.
We now witness its
original shape restored.
[HAYASHI] Ah. So the Great Word
is "Nothingness," is it?
Interesting for an M.J.B.K.
to come into being
without an ampule.
We owe that to Subete as well?
Pray tell, what is it that
binds your heart so tightly?
A dream? Or could it
perhaps be her?
So, yet another
human being vanished.
Stolen by one already gone.
For us poor
wretches left behind
there are few things
more anticlimactic.
Huh.
This place. It's familiar.
It's the place where
words come from,
the Logos World.
[gasps]
[M.J.B.K. 13A]
Mmmm...
What's going on?
What is that?
[SOUGON] At last,
it has become manifest.
Master Sougon!
[SOUGON] Behold the kanji
for "Nothingness" set free!
All concepts shall be erased!
Akira. I need a favor.
Hm?
Master Sougon.
Please, sir.
Permit me to speak
with you one last time.
You once said to me,
"Humankind is shackled
by the world of language,
words condemn man
to live a life apart."
And I understand.
Sometimes we can't see
the forest for the trees.
We mistake the word
for the thing.
But is that so wrong?
Is it weakness?
Do we live apart
when we can be moved?
Words can
break a heart, yes.
What we say to each other
can cut like a knife.
But the right words
can also make us laugh
or... fall in love.
People make the most
of what they have!
My dear. How very
humbling to see the manner
in which you've grown.
I wished to make you proud.
Grown into a feeble minded
wastrel poisoned by
the folly of those
she was sent to observe.
[gasps]
[SOUGON]
You understand nothing.
Yet you presume to
lecture me on the relationship
between mankind and language.
[MAIA]
No, not at all.
In the distant past we
invented the written word
to keep our thoughts
from being lost to time.
To convey feelings and ideas
that would otherwise
remain inaccessible
to future generations.
The selfsame motivating
force behind our need to speak
drove us to record and preserve.
And yet look at the cost
to modern society!
Language proliferates
without end!
"Social" media abounds in empty
buzzwords and bankrupt memes,
all vying for the
short attention spans
of an increasingly isolated,
infantile public
desperate to fill
the emotional void
left in the wake of
now meaningless words!
Such madness!
The tool has run amok
of its intended purpose.
What once ordered our
thoughts now scatters
and undermines them.
We live in a world
of superficialities.
It must be decimated.
Then and only then may Truth and
Utterance be reconnected.
[grunts]
That's not true!
Some people can't express
themselves without words!
What happens to them?
How do they "reconnect"?
[SOUGON] You've had your talk.
There's no more to discuss.
Why must it be this way?
No! You're wrong!
I can't stand here
and let you do this!
I'm sorry, but if
you won't listen to reason
you leave me no other choice!
I will... I will stop you.
[SOUGON]
Impossible.
[RANKO] When you asked me to
pick you up from the station,
I thought you were asking me
to pick you up from work.
What did you do,
sweetie, just hang out?
Didn't they have
anything for you?
Well, uh, you know how it is:
they just wanted to
go over some details
of the upcoming shoot.
You could've told me
you were coming here.
I was getting worried.
Sorry. Won't happen again.
[RANKO, KARAN scream]
What's happening?
I'm scared, Mommy.
[M.J.B.K. 13A]
Mmmm...
[SHOKO gasps]
Huh?
[SAKURAKO]
What's going on?
[SHOKO]
I'm not sure.
I feel like there were buttons
or something on here before.
Yeah, so. Don't s'pose
you remember how I
input commands on this thing?
No! We've lost a concept!
When a word vanishes
from the Logos World,
its corresponding concept
disappears from reality.
Gone. Erased from
our collective minds
like it was never there.
See, words give
people context.
They qualify our perception.
[WOMAN 13A screams]
[SAKURAKO] When we lose a word,
we lose a piece of reality.
If this keeps up, before long
we'll lose everything.
The world as we know it
will be reduced to a void.
When the concept
for "people" disappears,
we'll no longer even
perceive each other.
We'll cease to exist in the eyes
of our fellow human beings.
And that will be
the end of civilization.
[gasps]
Kenzaki! Sougon!
No. No more, please!
[yelps]
[KARAN]
Mommy!
Stop this!
--[M.J.B.K. 13A] Mu!
--[MAIA, AKIRA scream]
[SOUGON]
Farewell, world of words.
[M.J.B.K. 13A]
Mu! Mu! Mu mu! Mu! Mu.
[SOUGON]
"Subete" means "all things."
And here you are,
swallowed whole.
Rendered down
to nothing. Pathetic.
When every last concept
has been extinguished,
you shall become
at long last the key.
Provided, of course,
you are fit.
[grunts]
Why keep up the fight?
You can't have this.
I won't let you!
Why do you struggle?
The world is nearly
devoid of all concepts--
even now there's
nothing to fight for.
[KARAN]
I-- I don't get it.
She was just here a second ago.
Now she's gone.
Where--Where is she?
[HAYATO]
Hang in there!
Hayato, is that you?
[HAYATO] Akira's got this.
The world's in his hands!
Believe in him. He's fighting
to save us all!
We're not all that
different, he and I.
I became a politician,
he became a savior.
We wanted to change things.
Whatever I stand
to lose doesn't matter.
So long as there's
a shred of hope,
I have to go on fighting
for the good of mankind!
The same
holds true for all of us!
Milkman, is that--
is that you?
[HAYATO]
Our hopes. Our dreams.
If we cling to them, there's a
chance of turning this around!
[AKIRA] I'm not about
to let go! For I am...!
[HAYATO] Actually, the
world's in all our hands.
Each and every
one of us is a beacon!
[M.J.B.K. 13A]
Mu!
It isn't over!
I am... the savior!
[HAYATO] Yes! We all are!
Even in our darkest hour.
Something deep within us
continues to shine!
[AKIRA]
Damn right.
Heh. Well, lookie there.
[HAYATO]
That's reality.
Ours is the light that gives
the world its substance!
This is the word!
Ours is the voice!
[KARAN]
Hm!
[panting]
--[TSUTOMU] Kokone.
--[KOKONE] Guys!
[ALL]
Hm!
[SOUGON] Farewell. The tyranny
of words is at an end.
[chuckles]
[SOUGON]
You find it amusing?
I hear them. Do you?
Our friends won't be silenced.
Never. They're way too strong
and together unstoppable.
Time to save the day!
Genesis Merge! Dash form!
[TSUTOMU, HAYATO]
Jin!
Come on, guys!
We've got this!
Ha! Absolutely!
[AKIRA]
Shine on!
[MAIA, AKIRA, KOKONE]
Angel!
This ends now!
Give me back my love!
[M.J.B.K. 13A]
Mu mu mu!
[AKIRA, MAIA, KOKONE]
Moonlight Cannon!
[M.J.B.K. 13A]
Mu...
Ready when you are!
Beautiful blossom!
[AKIRA, KARAN]
Rin!
[M.J.B.K. 13A]
Mu!
[KARAN] Un, deux, trois.
Un, deux, trois.
Un deux. trois!
We can make it!
Let's fly!
[AKIRA, KOKONE]
Sei!
[HAYATO, KARAN]
Gai!
[AKIRA, KOKONE] Break through
the sound barrier!
[HAYATO, KARAN]
Wings of Calm Wind!
[M.J.B.K. 13A groans]
Pirouette!
Pierce it!
[AKIRA, MAIA]
Zai!
[TSUTOMU, HAYATO]
Ryu!
[AKIRA, MAIA]
Heat Haze Dance!
[TSUTOMU, HAYATO]
Break through!
[M.J.B.K. 13A]
Mu!
Ridiculous!
[AKIRA]
Shout it!
[AKIRA, MAIA]
Kou!
[M.J.B.K. 13A groans]
[AKIRA] Just when
the void envelops you,
you see what it is: A blank
canvas of endless possibilities!
[M.J.B.K. 13A]
Mu!
[BOTH]
Mugen Punch!
There are no limits!
We're free!
[grunts]
[M.J.B.K. 13A]
Mu!
[AKIRA]
Roar!
[AKIRA, HAYATO, TSUTOMU]
Phoenix!
[TSUTOMU, HAYATO, AKIRA]
Blood of a Passionate Heart!
Let it shine down
like the stars above!
Let it reach
across the firmament!
May it touch the eternal!
Soaring like a dragon!
Echoing like
the name of a king!
Our sound!
Our sacred song!
[GROUP]
Aquarion!
[MAIA] As long as we have
voices the world will endure!
[AKIRA]
Yes. For I am.
[ALL]
We are.
Each and every one.
[GROUP]
The saviors!
[M.J.B.K. 13A groans]
[breathing deeply]
Hm?
[SUBETE]
Maia!
[MAIA]
Subete.
[KARAN]
Where are Maia and Akira?
[TSUTOMU] Shouldn't we
all technically
be in the same place?
[HAYATO] In theory.
Perhaps the force return
program malfunctioned.
[grunts]
[SUBETE] I can see you.
Really see you.
Subete. What're you doing?
Please, come back. For me.
I need you.
I'm nothing on my own.
[AKIRA]
Maia?
Sougon Kenzaki.
Still think you're a threat?
Verbalize. Mu!
[AKIRA grunts]
Verbalize.
[SOUGON] Surely a creature with
so profound a gift as yours
can see the world
for what it is.
Words imprison the mind.
We use them not knowing
we but rattle the bars
of our own cages.
Look at us, boy.
We grope through a desert
on a path not our own.
That's weird.
I hear what you're saying.
But your voice
isn't coming through.
And let's be honest.
With or without language you've
never truly connected to anyone.
How lonely you
must've been. I'm sorry.
You know what
the real problem is?
You blame the world
for your own weakness.
Language might be
a prison for you,
but most people?
They use it to express
themselves, reach out.
Maybe we didn't
carve the path,
but we sure as hell
walk it on our own two feet.
[AKIRA grunts]
[SOUGON groans]
[coughs]
The kanji for "nothingness."
Originated aeons ago
from a pictogram
depicting a pair
of dancers embraced.
Even amidst the void
the human spirit dances still.
Akira!
Oh, no. Father!
Maia, look out!
Father! Where are you?
Speak to me!
[SUBETE] Akira Kaibuki. I was
meant to be the chosen one.
What did I do to you?
Why do you take
everything away from me?
I don't deserve this!
First Maia. Now my father.
Who the hell
do you think you are?
Nobody. Just the guy
who saves the world.
No! Bullshit! Bullshit!
Give me my Maia back,
you bastard!
[MAIA] Grow up.
That's not how it works.
You barely know who I am.
You've never really
seen me as a human being.
All you see is
a projection of yourself.
[SUBETE gasps shakily]
[MAIA] You might as well have
been looking into a mirror.
I'm a fantasy
for all these years,
just something
to put on a pedestal.
Something you wanted to be.
[SUBETE]
No. That's not true.
[MAIA] You're not
the person I used to know.
The boy who saved me all those
years ago in the moonlight.
He's long gone.
[gasps]
[rumbling]
[SOUGON groans]
This is futile.
Living by your own will,
cannot bring salvation.
--[SUBETE] Father!
--[AKIRA] Let's go.
[MAIA]
What? We can't just--
--[SUBETE] Father!
--[SOUGON] Akira.
--[SOUGON] Of course.
I remember.
[MAIA]
Master Sougon! Subete!
[screams]
No!
[CROWD chatters]
Huh, okay.
That's kinda strange.
Was I surrounded by darkness?
We defeated the M.J.B.K.
The concepts that were lost
have been restored.
[SHOKO]
That means we won, right?
[CROWD gasping]
Karan.
[OPERATORS gasp]
[ALL panting]
Hey! You kids okay?
Wait, where'd
Maia and Akira go?
[HAYATO] Iwagami,
put them onscreen!
[SHOKO]
Uh, right!
[beeping]
[ALL gasp]
[HAYATO]
Look!
All right!
[TSUTOMU]
Woo hoo!
[KOKONE]
What a ruh relief.
[SAKURAKO]
We actually did it.
Without having to play
our forbidden trump card.
You holdin' up okay?
[MAIA]
Yeah, I think.
[AKIRA] We can
talk later if you want.
For now, there's really
only one thing to say.
What's that?
One, two.
[ALL]
Welcome home!
[gasps]
[AKIRA]
We're back.
[MAIA]
Yeah! They know!
[SHOKO, KARAN, HAYATO, TSUTOMU,
SAKURAKO, KENTO laugh]
[chuckles]
[NESTA] Good to
have you back, legend.
[TSUTOMU] I notice
you haven't been drinking
much milk lately, Milkman.
[HAYATO] Will you
stop calling me that?
[AKIRA] What's the matter?
It's good for you.
You got something
against nutrition?
[HAYATO]
Not you, too! Cut it out!
[TSUTOMU]
Love the sarcasm, Savior Boy!
Good to see you loosen up
after the fighting's done!
[HAYATO]
Next: Episode Fourteen.
[TSUTOMU] "Show It!
You at Your Worst!"
[TSUTOMU] Yeah, we've still got
a lot more to get through.
[HAYATO]
It's not over just yet.
[AKIRA]
What's not?