[SAKURAKO]
Meow.
I don't know what to do.
For the Third Anniversary bash?
I'm sure you'll come up with
something super awesome.
Plus, you still have two days.
Don't forget, we have a freshly
written Reading Theater script.
Honestly, I imagine
that would suffice.
[TSUTOMU] No way, bro!
We gotta go all out!
Something bigger than
just a new Staged Reading!
Exactly!
We only get one third
anniversary after all,
so I want something a
little less run-of-the-mill
to celebrate such
an auspicious day!
[TSUTOMU]
Mh-hm.
That's why I'm thinkin'
we should make a movie!
Yeah! I say we make
a gory splatter-fest!
We'll have Tsutomu
get mauled by zombies.
Ooh! We should make
him explode, too!
Don't I have any
basic human rights?
I might enjoy a splatter movie.
Yeah? Zombies plus boom!
A movie.
Y'don't need to say what kind
of movie you want, Akira,
we already kno--
Oh, jeez, that was fast!
[KOKONE gasps]
That sounds nice.
If that's the movie we make,
I'd like to be the sword the
Savior pulls from the stone.
[giggles]
You aim too low. At least
play something living.
[KENTO]
Whoa! That's too much!
The eye! The eye! The eye!
[NESTA] When he vanishes
entirely, you'll be to blame.
She's trying to tell me
something, but what?
And that voice. I know
I've heard it before.
[gasping]
[MAIA]
Uh.
[KENTO sighs]
[MAIA laughs nervously]
[MAIA gasps]
Something wrong?
[MAIA]
Of course. I must... save Akira.
DEAVA was created
to resist Nesta
and the M.J.B.K.s.
If Akira's situation
is due to writing,
we must have data on it.
[gasps]
Took a pretty big risk, y'know.
Access files you're
not supposed to
and the security system
sets off an alarm.
[SAKURAKO]
Hm.
What were you doing in here?
And don't try to tell me you
wanted to play solitaire.
[MAIA sighs]
Commander, I find
myself in desperate need
of your assistance!
I ask because I
respect you as a man.
"As a woman"?
[SAKURAKO] From the outside, it
looks like an ordinary library.
But what lies beneath.
A secret government facility
dedicated to collecting
and studying a
variety of artifacts
from the ancient
writing culture.
There's so much.
Counting all the material
that's been excavated so far,
this vault is just
the tip of the iceberg
because the vast majority of it
has fallen into the
hands of Nesta.
Here you go, but
try to work quickly,
'cause if we get caught down
here, it's my butt on the line.
Don't worry about a thing.
If you get canned,
there's always a job
for you at Shirobaco.
[MAIA] I thought Kento was
already part of the café staff.
I advise DEAVA, as well
as manage this site.
Basically, I'm on loan
from the government.
[SAKURAKO]
If there's some kind of problem
going on with Akira's body,
it's highly likely it has
something to do with Vector-Ga.
[MAIA] I thought that
might be the case.
[KENTO]
It's our fault, then.
We knew the dangers that
machine represented.
[SAKURAKO] That's true. But he
piloted it of his own free will
in order to save the world.
So having regret for that choice
now does no good for anyone.
We've got to do the best we can.
We won't let him be
sacrificed. Not ever.
[MAIA]
Uh.
Oh. "We found this piece of art,
and believe it depicts
the Writing War."
There was a Writing War?
[SAKURAKO]
According to legend,
there was a time
when attuned people
could make manifest
the words they spoke.
For example, take
the word "rain."
By simply saying it, they could
create a torrential downpour.
[MAIA] No way. How
is that even possible?
[SAKURAKO] In the right
place, at the right time,
by uttering words filled with
the vibrancy of emotion,
they could gain access
to the World of Truth.
However, for those people,
the only option was to live
their lives moment to moment.
There was no means to leave
anything to future generations.
They wanted to leave behind
their wills, their dreams,
and this desire led them
to create a technology
of untold power.
[MAIA]
And that was?
[SAKURAKO] That was the
invention of writing.
With writing enabling
communication
with those far away, or
even later generations,
civilization was able to evolve
at an accelerated pace.
But there was one tribe
that felt this evolution
was dangerous.
They were worried, and
perhaps, rightly so,
that our reliance on
writing would lead us
to lose our connection
to the World of Truth.
[KENTO] Some wished to further
develop the culture of writing,
and they were opposed by those
who saw it as blasphemy
to the World of Truth.
Eventually, those disagreements
turned to conflict.
These altercations were the
beginning of the Writing War.
[MAIA]
I never knew.
Master Sougon never told
me about any of this.
He must've felt it wasn't
necessary for you to know.
To create blind followers, you
have to limit the knowledge
they have access to,
narrowing their point of view.
And that ghostly woman.
It seems she was
symbolic of something.
Of what exactly, we don't know.
However, the giants
you can see behind her
are referred to in the records
as the "Angels of Slaughter."
Ultimately, the
ancient war concluded
with the Writing Tribe
completely victorious.
Though most details of the
events leading up to that
were lost to the
ravages of time,
there is one thing we know
with absolute certainty.
We know what weapon
finally brought an end
to their conflict.
It's name.
Aquarion Logos.
Aquarion... Logos?
[MAIA]
What is this feeling?
Aquarion Logos. I know
that name... somehow.
[KENTO] In the end,
we never found anything.
[MAIA]
Commander, about Akira...
[SAKURAKO]
I know. Don't worry,
I won't say anything to
the other club members.
Including Akira himself.
You aren't tellin' him?
We could warn him about
the dangers of Vector-Ga,
and forbid him from using
it in future operations.
[MAIA]
It's pointless.
He'll keep fighting, no
matter what you tell him.
That's just who he is.
We'll be targeting
our female customers.
Women do love things that
are for a limited time only.
Y-Yeah! Th-They'll be
lined up out the door.
This menu should include
several healthy selections,
since those are quite
popular with the ladies.
When you say "healthy,"
are we talking salads?
Y'can't fill up on
a buncha leaves.
I vote we offer
something heartier.
Fried chicken, son!
No chance.
Not only are fried foods the
total opposite of healthy,
they add unnecessary prep time.
The chickens.
I could raise them.
We are not going to
start raising livestock!
I've got an idea, Big Bro!
We should add some hamburgers.
Just like a kid.
[KARAN growls]
Hush up!
[TSUTOMU]
Ah!
Hamburgers. Interesting.
Cows, huh?
We d-definitely don't have
room for you to raise those.
I know, let's merge the ideas,
and make healthy hamburgers.
[SAKURAKO]
Good call!
[KOKONE, SHOKO]
Huh?
This girl does
love a tasty burger!
All right then,
team, it's settled.
We'll all create our own
original healthy hamburgers.
[TSUTOMU]
What? We're actually doin' this?
Now let's get to work!
The boys' hamburger
platters are now complete.
Hayato's presentation is a tofu
burger. A twist on a classic.
Tsutomu's offering has
a r-rather unique shape.
What's this?
Some kinda meat loaf?
Prepare your tastebuds,
mademoiselles!
Making a burger
from tofu is cliché.
Being a true visionary, I
made tofu out of 'amburger!
That's just a hunk o' beef
shaped like a brick, weirdo!
Akira's looks pretty plain.
Well, it doesn't look bad, but
what matters is how it tastes.
[TSUTOMU]
What's this?
Okay.
[TSUTOMU]
Texture's unique.
It's low cal.
I didn't think edible
had to be specified.
Looks like Hayato's the only
boy who's got culinary skills.
Now it's time for the ladies
to show 'em how it's done!
Hurry along, now, Kokone
and Maia! Let's get to work.
Cooking's not really my--
Bet Akira'll dig it if you
make one especially for him!
[MAIA]
Huh?
[TSUTOMU]
Come on, genius!
--Try sampling a bit. Eat!
--Very well, I'll try some.
For they call--
Take it easy. I think
you're kneading it too hard.
Man... this is... tough.
Heh. Here try it more
like this, you got it?
Ah. Okay!
Oh yeah, just like you're
throttling an M.J.B.K.!
Whoa! I get it!
Stop it, Karan! You're
just confusing her!
Time to die M.J.B.K.!
Deathblow Strike!
Seriously, you are not helping!
[TSUTOMU]
Whoa! Awesome!
[HAYATO] Where'd you
learn how to do that?
That... looks yummy!
Hey! Why'd you
throw it all away?
I, uh, m-messed up.
Got the spices wrong.
N-No one wants to eat it.
It woulda been g-gross.
[MAIA]
I did it! It's ready!
So? What do you think?
Akira?
[AKIRA] I will find the way
to be the Savior of my tummy.
Yeah, keepin' the cliché alive!
You could've just
said it tasted bad!
Maia sure has come a
long way, hasn't she?
It makes me happy.
She's acting just the way
a girl her age should.
[phone beeping]
[ALL]
Uh?
[KENTO chuckles]
[gasps]
[AKIRA]
You used too many ingredients.
Oh, shut up. I'm making up
for it by buying groceries
to replace what got wasted.
You're so high maintenance.
Nobody asked you
to tag along, jerk!
Well, I'm here.
Yes, you are. I don't mind.
Take a break?
[MAIA]
Hm?
[TSUTOMU] They're sure
taking their time shopping.
They'd better not be off
whispering sweet nothings
to each other!
Why're you being so jealous?
You've got a cute girlfriend
standing right here.
Wait. What's this?
I made it separately from
the ones for taste testing.
Just for you!
Shoko!
Dodged ya!
But why?
[glass shattering]
[SAKURAKO]
Are you all right?
Yes. Sorry about this.
[SAKURAKO]
Did something happen?
No. I just feel a little
under the weather.
[MAIA]
This situation is... awkward.
I wanted to ask you a question.
[MAIA]
Uh?
It's about Subete Kenzaki.
Subete? Do you want to know what
kind of relationship we had?
[AKIRA] I can't let him
be better than me.
The next time we meet,
I'm taking him down.
To do that, I need to know
about him. That's why I asked.
Oh. So that's it.
That's what?
Never mind.
[AKIRA]
Hm?
His psyche is a bit
"uneven," you could say.
Subete's very intelligent, but
his immaturity holds him back.
So much that he can't
access his full power.
But he's still overconfident,
leaves himself open,
often lets his guard down,
and he's not very decisive.
You didn't list
any positive traits.
[chuckles]
Well it's not that
he's a bad person.
He had a lot going for him.
Like one time, long ago.
[AKIRA]
How long ago?
[MAIA] It all happened on
a beautiful moonlit night.
Much like this one.
I was suffering so much,
so hopelessly sad I
wanted to just disappear.
I was alone, crying,
and then he came to me.
I don't remember what Subete
said to me that night.
Whatever it was,
his words saved me.
They made me feel like it
was okay to go on living.
[AKIRA]
Hmm...
[MAIA]
What is it?
[AKIRA]
Nothing.
[MAIA] What? Are you
mad about something?
[AKIRA]
Nothing. Time to get back.
[MAIA]
Uh. Hey!
[AKIRA]
Is something wrong?
No, not at all.
Yeah?
You can't take him away.
I won't let you. Not Akira.
I won't let you
vanish. Not ever!
[BUSINESSMAN humming]
--[thud]
--[BUSINESSMAN grunts]
[MAIA] Nesta corporate
headquarters should have access
to plenty of resources
on the Writing Culture.
There must be a way,
some way to save Akira.
[MAIA]
This is odd.
They must've noticed
my intrusion,
but security's doing nothing.
[gasps]
[SUBETE]
You certainly took your time.
Hello, Subete.
Why do you look so surprised?
Surely, you knew I'd be here.
Even so, you deemed
me a pushover,
incapable of impeding
your progress.
I assume you plan to subdue me
and use me as a hostage
during your escape?
You've underestimated me, Maia.
How'd you--?
[NESTA]
How does he know?
I thought that much
would be obvious by now.
[MAIA gasps]
[NESTA] You had to have
realized that you are me.
[MAIA grunts]
That's nonsense!
How terrific.
I can't tell you what a relief
it is that you can see me.
Though I guess it
makes perfect sense.
[giggles]
I mean this is our
first proper meeting.
[GROUP] Cheers to three
years of business!
[OURA, OKAZAKI, SUZUKI,
TANAKA, SHOKO] Way to go!
It isn't time yet! Hard reset!
As long as Kokone's
here, it's always time!
Hayato! Can I eat
mine off your abs?
We're still waiting
on a few people.
Where are Maia and Akira?
This isn't like them.
Huh. Come to think of it,
Maia wasn't at Digibaco earlier.
I wonder where
she could've gone.
A-Akira, why?
[VECTOR-GA growling]
Didn't expect to see you again.
You thrust yourself alone,
into the breach, to
save Akira Kaibuki.
Your devotion is touching.
If you know something,
then just spit it out!
[NESTA] Akira Kaibuki
is slowly being erased,
due to the power you
refer to as Vector-Ga.
That accursed entity
devours concepts,
erasing their
meaning completely.
At the current rate,
the concept known as Akira
Kaibuki will simply disappear.
Do you understand what
this inevitability means?
With his concept lost, no one
will be able to see him.
He will become
wholly imperceptible.
And that's not all.
Eventually, his entire
existence will slip from memory.
The time you spent together,
the memories you shared,
they'll all be gone
without a trace.
Soon, Akira Kaibuki will cease
to exist. Even in your heart.
That can't be. Akira.
Are you sad? That's a pity,
since you have absolutely
no right to feel that way.
Didn't you know?
His disappearance is
entirely your fault.
Because Akira Kaibuki
is taking your place.
[VECTOR-GA]
Devour.
Not today. Stay put.
[VECTOR-GA]
I will devour.
[AKIRA] You're gonna stay
right where you are.
[NESTA]
Just remember,
the one the Vector-Ga
truly wants to erase...
...is you, Maia.
[gasps]
[NESTA]
Vector-Ga was initially created
as a counter-measure to
defeat Aquarion Logos.
And that unflinching sense of
purpose drives it ever forward,
even over the course
of 12 thousand years.
If that's true...
When the mighty Aquarion Logos
finally appeared during
the Writing War,
there were two
people piloting it.
One of those crew
members was me. Nesta.
[MAIA]
Nesta?
True love gave me the
strength to fight back.
I found that strength in my
co-pilot. My beloved Kiryu.
Ultimately, Aquarion
Logos fell in battle,
and Kiryu and I both perished.
But in the present day,
a man who desired our power
called out to us
across the void.
[SUBETE]
My father.
[MAIA]
Master Sougon?
[SUBETE] He yearned for
Aquarion Logos's power.
[NESTA] And so, after the
passing of 12 millennia,
he found the child born
under the right stars
to be the reincarnated Kiryu.
You can't mean.
Yes. Him.
Subete Kenzaki, former
Aquarion Logos pilot reborn,
the inheritor of Kiryu's legacy.
And...
[SOUGON] You were meant
to be with Subete.
This was your destiny from
the day you were born.
[NESTA] Using the remaining
fragments of my soul,
which had dissolved
into the Logos World,
he created a being to one
day act as the master key.
To unlock Subete's strength.
[MAIA]
I don't wanna hear this!
[RESEARCHER B]
He's doing it.
It's here!
Connection successful!
[SUBETE] Verbalism was the
catalyst in the reaction
that created you
from Nesta's soul.
A puppet on a string,
you could say.
That is exactly
what you are, Maia.
You're wrong. It can't be true.
To put it bluntly,
you're not even human.
You're no more than
a replacement for me.
My pretty puppet.
Nothing more than his puppet.
[NESTA laughing]
[MAIA]
Liar!
I didn't know it myself
until I took in the Book
of Verbalism's power.
No, it would be more appropriate
to say that I'd forgotten.
Every memory I had of your
origin had been sealed away.
Subete.
But now I remember everything
as clear as crystal.
Even how I created you
from the Logos World
as my father watched.
What's your earliest memory?
How about your parents?
Have you ever tried to
remember these things?
What's wrong? Nothing there?
You were created
as a blank slate.
There's nothing to remember.
Shut up! Stop it!
The rain. Did she
make that happen?
Now you can see
the Power of Truth.
Just being with Subete, you
were able to manifest a power
you never could've
found on your own.
Limited though it may be,
you've tapped into the
wellspring of my power.
But surely, even you
can see it by now,
see what you are at last.
[MAIA gasps]
[MAIA screaming]
You poor, wretched puppet.
I will at least bring it to an
end without further suffering.
Wow. It's raining cats
and dogs out there.
Poor widdle kitties!
And on our anniversary too!
[KOKONE gasping]
[KOKONE]
Akira! You-You're back!
Where's Maia?
What?
[SUZUKI, TANAKA scream]
[BOTH whimpering]
[SUBETE] Yes, it's time
to bring it to an end.
Our battle. Our very world.
[TSUTOMU]
Check it out, Shoko!
It's Okinawa's famous
chinsuko biscuits!
[SHOKO]
Wow!
[KARAN] You're way too
excited about that.
[TSUTOMU]
Butt outta my business!
I just wanna see my girlfriend
smile! Jeez, pipsqueak!
[KARAN]
Who you callin' pipsqueak?!
[SHOKO] If you brought
those for me, Tsutomu,
why're there crumbs
around your mouth?
[TSUTOMU cries]
[TSUTOMU]
Next: Episode 21!
[SHOKO]
"Tragic! An Immoral Gattai."
[KARAN]
Stupid lovebirds.