Ladies and gents!
The Verbalism Club
proudly presents:
The Shirobaco Reading Theatre!
And meow,
Let yourself be transported
or poor widdle
Sakurako will cwy!
[HAYATO]
"Twelve thousand years ago...
At a time when civilization
did not yet exist,
humankind lived
in harmony with Truth,
able to manifest their emotions
upon the physical world.
Drawing from the World of Truth
as you or I might
draw from a well,
merely by saying the
words 'rain' or 'wind,'
they could summon
torrential downpours
or fierce, howling gales.
They had only to speak
from the heart to make it so.
Alas, they held no means
of recording their emotions
or transmitting
them across time.
Thus did the written
word come to be,
and the world was changed.
Having attained a tool
by which one might speak
to future generations,
the development of civilization
as we know it was swift.
However,
a small tribe of dissidents
saw great danger in this tool."
"You play with fire!
Heed my words.
There will come a day
when the written word
shall bring great suffering!
This tool carries Truth
as surely as Falsehood,
and in times to come
will spread across
the face of the earth like
wildfire, robbing us of thought!
We must act!
For the sake of our souls,
we must seek
to abolish this scourge
once and for all!"
[HAYATO] "The Truth Tribe,
as they were called,
held nothing more
precious than mankind's
direct connection to Truth.
They warned of a time
when our reliance
upon the written word would
jeopardize that connection
and weaken our relationship
to the world as it really is.
[HAYATO]
Alas, seduced by its power,
mankind refused to let go of
this dazzling new technology."
"Don't speak of
a pitiful future!
Writing will advance us
into an age of prosperity!"
"Whosoever condemns writing
is an enemy of progress!"
Uh... "We'll never
abolish the written word!"
"We must protect it
with everything we've got!"
"We fight in the name
of mankind's legacy!"
"And so,
the Writing Tribe and the Truth
Tribe entered into conflict,
thus beginning a terrible war.
The Writing Tribe dwarfed
its enemies in number.
And yet, upholding the old ways,
the Truth Tribe boasted
an important advantage.
Their communion with the
World of Truth allowed them
to summon formidable allies
not of the earthly plane.
The Angels of Slaughter.
Worthy of their name,
the Angels wrought massacre
upon blood-drenched massacre.
The terrible war raged on,
both sides locked in deadly
intolerance toward the other."
"In the name of humanity,
the written word
shall be eradicated!"
All who oppose me will
share in its wretched fate!"
[HAYATO]
"Alas, one young man stood firm,
clinging to hope like driftwood
in an ocean of despair."
[CROWD screaming]
[NESTA gasps]
[NESTA]
What is this?
[NESTA] Such folly.
You cannot stand against us!
[KIRYU growling]
[NESTA gasps]
[NESTA yells]
You don't strike?
[KIRYU]
To have fear is to have heart.
And those who have heart,
I do not kill.
For I am...
...just a human being!
[HAYATO] "With that, the girl,
Nesta, and the boy, Kiryu, met,
and both tribes now knew
the human face of war."
"Can there exist such a man?
Why would he choose not to
slay his enemy given the chance?
I cannot understand.
Who is he? What does he desire?"
"I will not call another
human being my enemy."
"Today, I met him again.
He.... he does not
conceive of me as an enemy.
Why? I must strive
to know his mind."
"Writing and emotion are
of equal importance.
Both can foster connection."
[MAIA] "I met him
once again today.
Why, oh why, does
my chest always tighten
when I hear him speak?
This man. I must know
more about him!"
[AKIRA] "You are a purist,
m'lady. Too driven.
You stain your hands
in the blood
of perceived
enemies too readily."
"I now know his name. Kiryu.
A lovely sound.
Oh, indeed.
Why does it make me tremble?
Why does my heart race
when I say it?"
"Your name is Nesta.
Beautiful word. And strange.
The sound of it eases my mind."
"Kiryu! I would know you
better if fate decrees.
And be yet better known to you.
My inmost heart
I wish you to see."
"I still feel the warmth
of holding you close."
"Hold me again
with all your strength.
Let me break. Oh. Please."
"May this feeling
always be a part of me.
I am greedy. I long
for your heart and soul"
"Yes. I... I must say it!"
"Nesta, hear my words!"
[BOTH]
"I love you!"
[HAYATO] "A love transcending
tribal boundaries was born--
One the world could
not allow to flourish.
Their respective tribes urged
them to break the spell,
doing all they could
to rip them asunder.
But heedless of
impassioned warnings,
the two never let their
feelings for each other wane."
[NESTA]
So long as this war rages on,
our union will never have
the blessing of our peoples.
Let's end it.
With our powers combined,
let's end this war!
Very well.
Together, our voices will bring
peace to the whole world.
[NESTA]
Genesis.
[KIRYU]
Merge!
[KIRYU, NESTA]
Awaken, Aquarion!
[HAYATO]
"When their entwined voices
reached the World of Truth,
their hearts became as one.
Thus was summoned Aquarion!
Their combined power would
come to be known as Verbalism.
Logos emerged
to end the conflict
between word and feeling.
So fierce was its strength,
not even the Angels of
Slaughter could resist."
"Damn you, Aquarion Logos
and your infernal might!
I refuse to let it end
this way! Do you hear me?!
If their braided voices give
life to written word, so be it!"
I will devour not only the
writing, but its very concept!
"To withstand the awesome
power of Aquarion Logos,
the Truth Tribe
created a being
able to consume
the written word.
At its core, his creature,
a kind of anti-Aquarion,
moved under the impetus of
a vector known as Vector-Ga.
[HAYATO] Nesta was routed,
and taken captive,
cruelly imprisoned
by the Writing Tribe.
"Where is Kiryu? Is he alive?"
"Ah, Kiryu. You speak
of the ignominious traitor."
"Curse his name!
The fool was captured
by the Truth Tribe
and summarily put to death."
You speak lies!
Do I?
Word has it his head came off
with one fell stroke of the axe.
[NESTA crying]
[NESTA]
No...
[HAYATO]
"Pitiful excuse for a man,
letting himself be
killed over a woman.
Suppose now at least we know
the value of your love."
[NESTA crying]
Please, no...
[TSUTOMU] "He wrote this
just before his execution.
I thought you might
like to have a look at it.
[HAYATO] "Alas, having
rejected writing completely
as a member of the Truth Tribe,
poor Nesta could not
read the words."
What's it say?
That laying eyes on you
was the single greatest
misfortune of his life.
He goes so far as to say
your love poisoned his soul.
[NESTA gasps]
[KIRYU]
It was a mistake to love her.
That vile, treacherous woman
has led me to my doom!
Kiryu...
[KIRYU] If only I could turn
back time, never have met her!
I was a fool!
She did not deserve my love,
much less my life!
[NESTA]
No!
[MAIA sobbing]
"Such a miserable creature.
Let us send you to be with
your star-crossed lover
as a token of our mercy."
"Yes, in the company of that
deplorable Aquarion Logos."
"Her final punishment was to
be loaded into Aquarion Logos
and burned alive
in view of the people
to whom she'd hoped
to bring peace.
Yet, tethered to the
burden of her despair,
Nesta's spirit
could not move on.
In the wake of her
demise followed tragedy,
Nesta's anguish
and hatred lingered,
so great that they
tore an unbridgeable gap
between the World of Truth
and the written word--
A gap we call The Logos World.
The Truth Tribe,
now unable to exercise power
over the physical plane,
surrendered.
Victorious,
the Writing Tribe throve.
Since that day,
the culture of the written word
has grown exponentially.
Writing is now
the primary means
by which humankind
orients itself in reality.
The Logos World grew saturated,
and in time,
a society took shape
in which words and concepts
were inextricably linked."
And so, this tragic
tale of lovers
in the midst of war
comes to a close.
Yes...
[ALL] A legend that could
not become a legend.
[applause]
[MAIA]
Found it! With this, I can...
[NESTA]
You can what, exactly?
[MAIA] I'm getting
out of here! I'm going home!
To the man who made it possible
for me to live in this world!
[NESTA]
You poor, wretched fool.
However strongly you feel,
don't you realize
the man's probably long
forgotten you by now?
[MAIA]
That's not true!
People betray
one another so easily.
Love, for all its sweetness
and light, is hollow in the end.
For some, maybe,
but he made me a promise!
Whatever happens, I'll save
the world! That's a promise!
I believe his voice
with all my heart!
Oh? And whose voice
would that be, my dear?
Whose voice?
[NESTA giggles]
Akira Kaibuki
must be quite the man
for you to lose
his name so quickly.
Ah, but you see, your love
for him is chipping away
at that love's existence,
piece by tiny piece.
[MAIA whimpering]
[NESTA]
The more someone cares for him,
the sooner his concept is erased
from their mind altogether.
[MAIA groans]
[MAIA]
I am going home.
[NESTA]
But why?
Why go to such lengths for a man
whose name you
can't even hold on to?
Because he's... important.
I have to go back.
Even if I don't remember,
I know.
In my heart, I know.
A memory is loveliest when
it remains trapped in the past.
Why do I find myself envious?
Shall I end her life?
I only jest!
Subete...
[SUBETE]
See her back to her room.
[KOKONE gasps] He won't exist
anymore? Th-That's awful!
Between what Maia told me
and her sudden difficulty
remembering pertinent
details about him,
I'm afraid we have no choice
but to assume that's the case.
I blame Vector-Ga.
I'm so sorry, Akira.
We've known that damn thing
was dangerous from--
[AKIRA] I needed its power,
plain and simple.
I regret nothing.
[KARAN] How can you stand
there and talk like that?
You just accept it?
That you'll be erased?
She has a point, Kaibuki.
Surely you don't mean
to go on fighting
despite the risk
to your very existence!
[AKIRA]
I do.
I promised Maia
that'd I save the world.
I am The Savior.
I understand the source of
Akira's extraordinary Verbalism.
At least I suspect I do.
This world shrinks from
people who speak their minds
or who are earnest
about how they feel.
They make us uncomfortable.
It's always been that way.
The more straightforward someone
is, the more off-putting.
[SAKURAKO]
But you...
Whatever reaction you got,
you'd go right on
saying what you felt,
telling us you were The Savior.
That voice is supported
by an unshakeable will.
Hence, you have
bottomless reserves
from which to
support your Verbalism.
[KOKONE gasps]
[MAIA]
There was the first time we met.
He forcibly pulled my Vector
in and merged with me,
and then what else?
[MAIA]
Tanabata! Yes!
We made a giant paper
mache display together.
With, um,  Kokone
Kikogami, Hayato Kujyo,
Tsutomu Domon,
Karan Uminagi, and...
Why?
[MAIA]
Why?!
No...
Shizuka, dear, why
have you set a third place?
[SHIZUKA]
Don't be silly, it's for--
Oh, well isn't that strange.
[MAIA] I will not forget.
I will not forget.
I will not forget!
[KARAN gasps]
[AKIRA]
For I am... The Savior
[MAIA] Yes, The Savior.
But what's your name?
I know it! I have to know it!
[crying]
Why can't I remember?!
[SUBETE] Our memories
of that moonlit night
are no more than
pure fabrication.
Be that as it may,
the things she did for me...
Like supporting me through
the worst of our childhood...
That's true.
Our relationship may
have been founded on a lie,
but the time we've spent
together is still fact.
My feelings for her,
in spite of everything,
are unquestionably real.
Unquestionably, eh?
How did I fare
as a fake relative?
All things considered, I mean,
was I convincing?
[BABY SUBETE crying]
[MAO] Oh, wait, Shintarou,
not quite yet.
Wait till your nephew smiles.
Ugh. Is a picture
really necessary?
Don't be obtuse.
This is a special occasion,
of course it is!
[MAO]
Ooh! Here we go!
Hurry, before he
gets restless again.
[HAYASHI]
Uh, right.
[SUBETE] Even if it
means hurting Maia,
there remains only
one path open before me now.
Akira Kaibuki...
I will see you defeated!
[coughs]
With my name. My existence.
My everything on the line!
[M.J.B.K. croaking]
[SAKURAKO]
You're telling me every word
in the Logos World
has begun to distort?
Oh my god.
[KARAN]
What's gonna happen?
[KENTO] Once the distorted
words are absorbed
by the giant M.J.B.K.,
their concepts will disappear,
just like with Nothingness.
Except even faster!
[HAYATO]
I'll launch immediately!
[SHOKO]
You can't!
The corrosion density of
that space is off the charts!
If you plunge into that,
even with a Vector,
your existence will warp
beyond recognition!
S-So does that mean...?
It's him.
All of the kanji
representing all our names
will have gone rogue.
You and your vectors will
be devoured by the M.J.B.K.
Well then obviously we can't go!
I can.
That thing's power
stems from warping the kanji
for the word "everything."
My name doesn't
mean anything anymore.
Verbalize.
[SHOKO] I'm getting activation
signals from all Vectors!
[HAYATO]
But who's controlling them?
[KARAN] We're all
right here. Who can it be?
[phone ringing]
[KOKONE]
Th-The Aquariphone!
What is this?
I think this word's important...
It's a word that
led us all forward.
That's right!
We have a friend in there!
We have to help!
[KOKONE]
You c-can't go alone!
[HAYATO]
This is so typical of him.
[KARAN] Yeah!
You can't hog all the glory!
You guys...
But if you are the
only one who can do it,
then we believe in you!
Just come back in one piece.
And when you do,
prepare to get an earful.
And a buncha bonks
from my Pico Hammer!
Sorry the adults
are so useless, buddy.
We're all counting
on you, though!
Go kick some ass!
Godspeed!
Get out there and
make good on that promise!
Akira Kaibuki launch!
[HAYASHI] I've loaded your
precious Maia onboard.
I had to be somewhat
less than delicate,
but it's safer this way.
Once the writing in
the Logos World vanishes,
everything will be ready.
All you'll have to do is
trigger the annihilation pairing
with Aquarion Logos.
[SUBETE] And the culture of the
written word shall fall to ruin,
as will everything born of it.
[HAYASHI] The end is
only a matter of time.
Do you suppose there's anyone
left foolish enough to stop you?
[SUBETE]
I certainly hope so.
A fool who upholds his
lost cause to the bitter end
is a fool I dearly want to see.
[HAYASHI]
Subete.
I've always maintained a certain
professional distance from you,
have I not?
Yes. Why?
Forgive me if it's hardly
my place to say this,
but nonetheless...
Well, do your best.
[SUBETE]
I'm headed out.
[M.J.B.K.]
Su... be... te!
Is he here?
In the beginning
was the word.
Alpha and Omega.
Genesis Merge. Give praise!
Genesis Merge! Savior!
Aquarion!
He's here.
[SUBETE]
Logos!
[AKIRA]
Deava!
I can hear his voice.
But what is his name?
I may not remember,
but that voice...
...that voice... is amazing!
[M.J.B.K.]
Su... be... te!
Subete Kenzaki. Set Maia free!
Akira Kaibuki. Let's end this!
[SAKURAKO] To think I'd
have to rely on you poor kids
till the very end!
I'm in the wrong line of work.
[SHOKO]
I think the Calligraphy Class
is looking for instructors.
[SUBETE] When she was
Father's secretary,
he always complained
about her handwriting.
[SAKURAKO] I thought we agreed
not to bring that up again!
[SUBETE]
Writing's a window to the soul!
[SAKURAKO] What exactly
are you trying to say?
[SHOKO]
Next time, Episode 25.
[SUBETE]
"Gather! Voices for Tomorrow."
[SAKURAKO]
Someone get me an Aquaripen!