Get away!
[panting]
You're not worthy of her!
[SOUGON]
I was wrong.
This is not the great word
as I'd hoped.
[yells]
[HAYASHI] Yes,
something's definitely off.
I'm afraid this isn't the
"mighty word to be born
of the whirling vortex"
you mentioned.
Why did a different word
come out instead?
[SOUGON]
It was Subete.
His force of will reshaped
the emerging word.
Now. Verbalize.
I'm coming!
I can do this!
[M.J.B.K. 12A]
Ri.
Good job, Hayato!
Let's go, Karan!
[rock mudic plays]
[HAYATO, KARAN]
Wings of the Calm Wind!
[caws]
[KARAN]
We did it, Big Brother!
Way to keep us
on the edge of our seats!
[beeping]
Guys, wait! Look!
Something's wrong!
Odd. I've never
seen it do this.
[KARAN gasps]
What is that thing?
[SUBETE]
Tornado Strike!
[HAYATO, KARAN scream]
We'll settle this once
and for all. Akira Kaibuki.
[SOUGON] In times past,
humanity was at one
with the world of truth.
But the written word,
for all we prospered from it,
wrought incalculable suffering.
[FEMALE OPERATOR 1A]
Unlocking launch sequence.
Raising electromagnetic catapult
deck by five points a second.
[MALE OPERATOR 1B]
Sensors indicate clear skies...
Thrusters should be
fully charged
in the next twenty-five seconds.
[SHOKO] Vectors One,
Two, and Three,
prepare for immediate launch!
[SAKURAKO] Another
M.J.B.K. space opened
unannounced during the fight.
Why did we fail to detect it?
[SHOKO] After effects of
the Whirl M.J.B.K. caused
interference in our Field
Detection apparatus,
and several other systems.
[SAKURAKO] Subete.
What're you up to?
[AKIRA]
Verbalize.
Those Vectors
are pink and blue.
It isn't him. Oh, well.
[SUBETE]
I'll have to drag him out!
[HAYATO] He's splitting off
parts of his body
to attack us on all sides!
It's going to be dangerous,
but if we can get in close.
We'll cut right
through this turkey!
[HAYATO, KARAN yell]
Don't get so grabby!
Now back off!
[HAYATO, KARAN groan]
[HAYATO] Long range attacks
and close range deflection?
So that's how it is.
[SUBETE]
Here they come.
[AKIRA]
Genesis Merge!
[KOKONE]
Shine bright!
[ALL]
Aquarion!
[AKIRA, MAIA, KOKONE]
Angel!
Be careful, guys!
Distance means nothing
with that thing's attacks!
[KOKONE]
Wh-What does that mean?
[SUBETE]
Tornado Strike!
[AKIRA grunts]
Huh!
He bounced it back!
[AKIRA, MAIA gasp]
[KOKONE groans]
[AKIRA grunts]
Kaibuki, heads up!
[screams]
Stop, Subete! Why would
you help the M.J.B.K.s?
Have you actually thought
about what it would mean
to eliminate words
from this world?
[SUBETE]
Hey, Red Vector pilot.
Akira Kaibuki!
Leave Maia alone!
I said get away from her!
[MAIA gasps]
What is it?
Look out!
[inhales deeply]
[KOKONE] No. They're...
They're leaving me!
All those things I wanted.
All my dreams.
Pull it together!
Don't give up!
A psychological attack!
[KOKONE] N-No!
It's all f-falling apart!
[M.J.B.K. 12A]
Ri...
Their Merge broke!
She split off!
--[screaming]
--Karan!
[KARAN continues screaming]
I see now.
The M.J.B.K. has revealed
the true desires deep
in your hearts to me!
You have separate wants!
All of you do!
It's no use! We can't
keep fighting like this!
Then break off
and pull back!
Fortunately, the word corrosion
rate has slowed to a trickle.
We should have more than
enough time to regroup
and come up with
a new attack plan.
[BOTH gasp]
[TSUTOMU] What do you think
you're doing, bro?
The Commander
gave the retreat order!
[AKIRA] A threat to
our world still exists.
I cannot leave him unchecked!
This is completely nuts!
[groans]
[MAIA]
Akira.
[SUBETE]
Get away!
Our Vectors! He split
them up somehow!
[SUBETE] Time to end this.
Special Delivery, you bastard!
[SUBETE grunts]
[gasps]
[exhales sharply]
[HAYATO groans]
[AKIRA]
Hayato, but why?
Taking that hit
was the best strategy.
Keeps you in the fight.
[squelch]
Shoko, force withdrawal
for all Vectors!
That's an order!
Right!
Where are you going?
[SUBETE] I've exhausted too
much of my Verbalism Ability.
But. I learned something here.
I learned
that I can defeat you!
[TSUTOMU] So Maia, are you
and the other ladies okay?
[MAIA] Yeah. Apparently
the psychological attack
was only a temporary affliction.
It's not
affecting us anymore.
But he's not that fortunate.
[KARAN]
Big Brother.
I... I g-got taken out of
the fight so quickly.
It's my fault he's in there.
It's not.
Or is your ego
so swollen that you'd
trade your comrades' lives
for personal glory?
Akira.
[WOMAN 12A panting]
Oh, there he is!
[chuckles]
[SHOKO] So far,
this M.J.B.K. doesn't seem
to have caused
any major damage.
The word corrosion rate
has only climbed
one percent over
the last two hours.
I didn't know M.J.B.K.s
could work like this.
[FEMALE OPERATOR 9A]
There's been no change
to gravity potential of the
enemy inside the Logos World.
It seems to have stopped moving.
For all intents
and purposes...
My shoulders are stiff!
You should probably get
a little rest too, you know.
Yes, you're right.
That sounds pretty nice.
[SAKURAKO] With the
Vectors being repaired,
this stagnation is a big help.
Still wish I knew
what stopped the corrosion.
[SOUGON] From his
performance thus far,
it is more than possible
we have found the chosen one.
[gasps]
[SOUGON] You could never hope
to win against the chosen one.
Not against the man
in the red Vector.
No! He's not the chosen one!
[HAYASHI] He's suppressing
the M.J.B.K.'s power,
yet still maintaining
his fusion with it.
It allows him to mitigate
the strain on his body,
and at the same time stall out
the word corrosion rate.
All in all, rather
impressive, I'd say.
[SOUGON] This new word Subete
has spawned into being
was transformed from the great
word spoken of in prophecy.
But as yet, its
alteration is incomplete.
If his psyche shows weakness
during this critical juncture,
what happens then?
Tell me, Subete. Will you
have what it takes?
Can you pull the trigger
that will change the world?
[MAIA] There's something
massive out there,
and it's coming.
Or is it just biding
its time? Waiting to strike.
[door clicks open]
Who's there?
[microwave dings]
[MAIA]
Akira! What the hell?
Y'want some?
[MAIA] What are you
even doing here?
You were told to go home and
wait for further orders.
There's no telling
when we're going to be
called back into action.
Makes sense for me
to just stay here.
Go on.
Are you doing all right?
After what happened to Hayato.
[AKIRA]
There was something he said.
"What do you mean when
you say you're the savior?"
"What do you expect back from
the world you're saving?"
[AKIRA]
There's nothing.
[MAIA]
Mm?
It's my dream, to be
the man who saves the world.
But the reason why, though,
is something I'd never
thought about.
What comes afterwards, either.
That was it. I tried to
really concentrate on it.
But there was still nothing.
Instead, ask why
you're so obsessed.
Why you're so driven
to be a savior.
I'm not sure. But hey!
Not knowing doesn't
stop me from wanting it!
No matter what happens.
I have to be the savior.
It's my-- my only...
[MAIA]
Akira?
[AKIRA snoring]
Um. Come on!
Well, at least
he smells nice.
[birds chirping]
[KARAN] Let go of me!
You're hurting my arm!
Let go!
[SAKURAKO]
Akira, stop this instant!
[AKIRA] Time to get
in your Vector, Karan.
We're launching.
[TSUTOMU] Launch?
Are you kidding me?
The Vectors
aren't even fixed yet!
Yours and Karan's
are still damaged!
Long as they fly,
no problem.
Ow! Let go!
P-Please stop!
Someone'll get hurt!
Do you have any plan
for dealing with this M.J.B.K.?
Something about its power
makes Merging useless.
I hope you've come up
with a solution.
I'll just have to
figure that out on the way.
Should worse come to worst,
we crash any unusable
Vectors into the enemy.
[ALL gasp]
What the hell are you
talking about, dude?
They'd never even make it
without someone inside
piloting them!
Then I'll stay behind.
If that's what it takes
to save the world,
I'll gladly make that sacrifice.
[running footsteps]
Would you listen
to yourself?
[gasps] Akira! No.
Tell me you're joking.
You can't--I mean, shouldn't--
even talk like that.
Please don't go.
You're why we lost...
remember?
[gasps]
[AKIRA] If you're gonna
get in my way, go to hell.
[KOKONE]
Y-You can't mean it.
That's quite enough of that.
Hayato is of
no further use to us.
So, Karan Uminagi. I need you.
[KARAN] No further use?
What're you saying?
He's my friend!
[AKIRA] You need to shut up
and do what I tell you.
For I am...
[TSUTOMU]
That's it!
I refuse to let
anyone use the Vectors
like their own
personal property.
Take Akira Kaibuki
to the holding cells.
[clang, click]
Akira, what are you thinking?
[sniffling]
[SAKURAKO] What is wrong
with that kid?
Akira. W-Why?
Fine, go then.
--[machines beeping]
--[KARAN sobbing]
Stupid Akira!
[clock ticking]
[SUBETE]
Time for round two.
[M.J.B.K. 12A]
Ri.
[FEMALE OPERATOR 1B]
Deflection pulse detected...
[MALE OPERATOR 1B]
Commander! M.J.B.K. influence
detected in DEAVA base!
[SAKURAKO]
What happened?
[SHOKO] All of a sudden,
the word corrosion rate
started increasing rapidly!
[SAKURAKO]
What?
What the? I could've
sworn I was in my room.
Uh.
The hell?
Wasn't I at Shirobaco?
[KOKONE]
Huh?
Huh? Wait, what?!
[SHOKO] And the next thing
you know, you're in Asakusa?
You sure it wasn't a dream?
[TSUTOMU]
It wasn't a stupid dream!
I'm wide awake, all right?
Anyway, I'm heading back,
but I'm broke.
So pay my train fare for me!
[TSUTOMU] What the?
Whoa, déjà frickin' vu!
[KOKONE panting]
Th-That's weird.
I'm back here!
Gotta hurry back to base
before they worry about me!
Huh? Where am I,
the Twilight Zone?
[MAIA] Why is it taking so
long to get to Shirobaco?
The M.J.B.K.'s active
but why now?
Only one reason
I can think of.
[beeps]
[GUARD 12A]
Hey, you.
--[thud]
--[GUARD 12A groans]
[AKIRA]
Verbalize.
[MECHANIC 12A]
Hey, you, get back here!
We haven't
finished repairs yet!
Vector One has
just launched, Commander!
I knew it. Taking advantage
of the M.J.B.K.'s power.
He distanced himself
from the others.
[SHOKO]
What do you mean?
[SAKURAKO] Akira pushed us away.
Creating an emotional gap
between him and
the rest of the pilots.
The M.J.B.K. took
full advantage of that,
translating that emotional
distance into physical space.
[SHOKO] Why would he do
that on purpose?
[SAKURAKO] The only reason
that makes sense is that
he wanted to fight alone,
without getting
the others involved.
[MAIA] So that's
what he had planned.
What an imbecile!
[SAKURAKO] I thought
his sudden attitude shift
was totally out of place,
but I never knew
he'd take things this far.
[SHOKO] But there's no way
he can beat an M.J.B.K.
with a single Vector!
[SAKURAKO] I assume
Akira is aware of that.
I'm sure that in his heart
of hearts, he's waiting.
Waiting for someone
who's still willing to
try to bridge
the gap between them.
[MAIA panting]
Idiot! Moron! Damn you!
I never learned how to give up,
and I'm not gonna start!
[SUBETE] Coming at
me solo? Are you nuts?
D'you know, Subete.
The etymology of
the kanji for "separation"?
It's a bird and a snake.
Both intertwined
and inseparable.
That's one theory on how
this kanji came to be.
[AKIRA] So, I will
become the bird,
and peck this kanji away!
[SUBETE] Trying to bust my kanji
into its constituent parts?
It won't work!
Oh no!
He can't access enough
of his Verbalism Ability!
[SUBETE] Give it up!
I've already won!
Maia?
[thud]
[SUBETE] What are you doing,
Maia? It's over now!
That Kaibuki jerk is gone.
You're free now, you can
return home with me.
[MAIA]
Akira. Do you read me?
[SUBETE]
That's their comms.
So, am I picking them up because
I swallowed the Red Vector?
[MAIA]
You're always too obstinate
for your own good, you know?
But I could never let you
do this on your own.
That's why... I made the
decision to go with you.
[SUBETE]
Maia, why?
[MAIA] It took some time,
but I've finally come
to the realization that
you're the only one for me!
Yes, ever since then.
Subete just couldn't cut it.
It had to be you!
[SUBETE]
Maia, what are you saying?
What I mean is.
I want to Merge with you!
Akira!
No, don't!
Get away! Stop it!
Get away from her
this instant!
[grunts]
Genesis Merge!
Shout it out!
[BOTH]
Aquarion!
[MAIA] Yes. I never want to be
separated from you again.
Because. Merging
with you, feels so good!
[AKIRA, MAIA]
Kou!
[SUBETE yells]
[SUBETE grunts]
I hate you, Kaibuki!
I will finish this.
I swear on my life.
[KARAN] I've got
the decorations ready!
[MAIA] And I just want to try
throwing someone in the air!
[KOKONE] What are you
talking about?
[AKIRA] I've already bought
a daruma doll for us!
[KARAN]
I wanna draw in the eyes!
[MAIA] We're all getting
ready for the launch!
[KOKONE] Are you sure?
Don't get carried away, now!
[AKIRA]
Next: Episode Thirteen.
[AKIRA, KARAN, KOKONE, MAIA]
"A Great Victory! Our Savior."
[KOKONE] Do you guys really
think we have a shot at winning?