Genesis Merge. Give praise!
Genesis Merge. Savior!
[BOTH]
Aquarion!
I can hear his voice.
But what is his name?
I may not remember,
but that voice...
...that voice... is amazing!
[M.J.B.K. A]
Subete!
Subete Kenzaki. Set Maia free!
Akria Kaibuki. Let's end this!
[SUBETE yells]
Society's Achilles' Heel.
Modern man is only
capable of understanding
what can be put into words.
When the Logos World vanishes
and takes written
language with it,
the concepts that define
us will cease to exist.
Civilization will at
last come to an end.
[AKIRA]
Give Maia back, you bastard!
[SUBETE]
Over my dead body!
[AKIRA yells]
Seven years ago, the efforts
of Sougon Kenzaki
drew my body from the
Logos World and created you,
a makeshift vessel for
my spiritual essence.
In doing so, he radically
destabilized the balance
between that sphere and
the physical plane.
Balance?
[NESTA] The Logos World
is a fusion of my Self
and the Aquarion Logos
of ages past.
Remove me from the equation,
even if only in body,
and the delicate
equilibrium unravels.
Consequently, things began to
go awry in the Logos World
and written language became
hopelessly distorted.
Sougon exploited the mockery
kanji had become as a result
and created M.J.B.K's to
further upset the balance.
Of course.
It's your fault.
From beginning to end, my dear.
[NESTA laughs]
[gasps]
Even so,
I have every faith in
the promise he made to me.
[NESTA]
I'm afraid this will not do.
Are you in pain?
I'm more than happy to help.
What are you doing? Stop that.
[NESTA] This power you inherited
from Kiryuu... [chuckles]
I'll be borrowing it.
Verbalize.
[M.J.B.K. A]
Subete!
Sou!
I can't let you live.
You're a threat.
To everything!
Go on! I'll be damned if
I let you become a Savior!
[AKIRA]
Subete!
[SUBETE]
You're only reward in all this
will be watching the
world you love end!
[gasps]
[AKIRA]
Maia.
That's not with this is about.
It's not the world I love.
[SUBETE]
What?!
It's the world where
Maia can be free!
Well I won't let her go!
[coughs]
[gasps] Oh, no.
Damn it.
Damn it all!
Please don't go.
[cries]
[MAIA]
He's gone.
[MAIA sobs]
The... The one I cherish.
The only thing that gave
my life any meaning.
Maia.
Isn't that a shame?
Without the Book of Verbalism,
neither of you can even register
the poor fool's existence.
Aren't you pair?
Nothing left to do now but lick
each other's wounds, I suppose.
I knew in my heart
this would happen.
I am sorry, but I had
to go through with it.
Even though it meant
hurting you.
[MAIA crying]
I don't expect forgiveness.
All I ask is that you let
me tell you one last thing.
The Truth, Maia.
I love you with every
fiber of my being!
[NESTA] The Logos World
is the embodiment
of both my hatred and
of Aquarion Logos.
An annihilation reaction
can only be catalyzed
by its complete opposite
The antithesis of hatred.
Undying true love!
Bring this world to a fitting
end, Aquation Logos of Love!
[MALE VOICE A]
It's gonna be fine.
[BOY A]
Mm? Who's there?
[FEMALE VOICE A] Are you hurt?
You must be lonesome.
[FEMALE VOICE A] But there's
no reason to worry.
[FEMALE VOICE B]
You and I are one and the same.
[NESTA] A world free
of written language.
Whereas mankind
could touch reality
only through abstraction,
with their cognitive
crutch kicked away,
the line separating "I"
and "Thou" is obliterated.
Harmony is restored.
The discrete consciousness
of each individual
gives way to unity.
We begin to see ourselves and
our fellow travelers as One.
Love and compassion prevail.
All is beauty!
And it is sublime!
I'm kidding, naturally.
Any possibility of that perished
with the invention of writing.
Harmony is a lost cause.
Modern man cannot
establish his identity
in absence of the written word.
[WOMAN A, MAN A]
Huh?
Absorbed in the pleasures
of genuine connection,
the human spirit
will gently ebb away.
You had it coming. Ta-ta.
[SUBETE]
What is this?
Where am I?
Indeed. Do you even have
the right to be here?
The sum of your life's work
was to childishly force your
love onto someone else.
All that potential, and what
do you have to show for it?
Don't be so hard on him.
Subete did the best he could.
You saw it with your own eyes.
Now that everything
important to you is lost,
in your heart, do you regret the
failure or the ambition itself?
[SUBETE]
Father, I...
[MAIA]
It's deserted.
[FEMALE VOICE B]
Come to us, please.
I want you to know how we feel.
[MALE VOICE A]
Be connected.
Stay away!
[FEMALE VOICE A]
You've lost something important.
You're hurting.
[MALE VOICE B]
It's gonna be all right.
[MAIA] Stop it! Get out
of my head, all of you!
I am Maia Tsukigane!
I will not become part
of whatever you are!
[MAIA]
What?!
[MALE VOICE A]
This way. Over here.
[FEMALE VOICE A laughs]
Oh, don't bother,
writing doesn't make
sense to you anymore.
It's just a bunch of
meaningless squiggles.
[NESTA]
Completely useless.
You'll never understand.
I know this.
You know, but you understand
no more than I.
[MAIA]
And yet, it's familiar.
This is my... my...
[NESTA]
No! Impossible!
[screaming]
[MAIA] I know.
And I don't want to forget.
I don't want to lose it.
That's why I'm here.
That's my purpose. To accept it!
To give it voice!
Akira!
[AKIRA]
Maia!
[MAIA gasping]
You actually made it back.
Wherever I'm needed, that's
why I'm called... the Savior.
Your savior.
[M.J.B.K. A]
Subete!
Why won't you disappear?!
Damn you!
Maia's will brought me back.
As long as someone feels
something for me,
and has a voice to call it
out, I'm not going anywhere.
Wretched puppet!
Your voice is worthless!
Somebody sounds jealous.
[NESTA]
You know nothing!
[SUBETE]
I...
[SOUGON, MAO]
Subete, you must...
Protect the one you love.
Strike down your fated enemy.
Mm?
Must we always be at odds?
Apparently.
[MAO] A man stands up for
his love and protects it.
[SOUGON] A man must clear
the field of adversaries
before he has the
luxury of love.
[sighs]
How typical.
But, thanks for the advice.
You didn't think I would
just let you run away.
I'm not exactly running.
Damn it, you don't get to
waltz off, acting all smug.
Arrogant prick. You can vanish
when I've beaten you!
Everyone, please.
This is ridiculous.
What is the matter
with you people?!
[M.J.B.K. A]
Sou!
[BOTH]
Keep your hands off Maia!
Subete, you imbecile! Do you
not realize what this means?
Yeah, I do!
So go right ahead and accuse
me of being a flake!
If that's my truth,
I gladly embrace it!
[AKIRA] Oh, that's good.
I like that.
[SUBETE]
What?
[AKIRA]
Let's do it. Ultimate Verbalism.
[ALL]
Aquarion!
[SUBETE] I.... I don't know that
I'm comfortable with this.
[AKIRA]
Relax. Just let it happen.
[MAIA] It feels like
you're at heavens' door.
[AKIRA, MAIA, SUBETE]
It's amazing!
Logos Genesis!
This power,
where is it coming from?!
[AKIRA, MAIA, SUBETE]
Mugen Blade!
You little bastards!
[M.J.B.K. A]
Su... be... te!
Hang on, is it just me or were
we in the middle of something?
It feels like we were living
in some terrible dream.
[HAYATO]
What the--?
[KOKONE whimpers]
[NESTA] How can an
M.J.B.K. and Aquarion
exist on this plane together?
[CROWD MEMBER A]
What the hell is that?
[CROWD MEMBER C]
Run! It's a monster!
[CROWD MEMBER B]
Some kinda robot.
[CROWD MEMBER D]
Has to be an illusion.
[NESTA]
Now you've done it.
Let the hate flow through you!
Verbalize!
I won't lose.
Not to you imbeciles!
[AKIRA]
That's a solid voice.
Uh. We can't throw it off!
She simply has better Verbalism
ability than we do!
Stronger than the
three of us combined.
But if we added a few more...
You've got this!
[HAYATO]
Hang in there, guys!
We're counting on you!
This isn't over yet!
[KARAN]
We're with you all the way!
[SHOKO] You can hear us,
right? Go get 'em!
[KENTO]
You can do it!
All right. We hear
ya loud 'n clear!
That's what I call backup!
Now we've got this!
Timing's everything, bro.
Let's get to the punch line.
Hit 'em where it hurts!
Don't even think about losing!
Take it down!
You're the Savior, remember?
We're with you, Akira!
We're sayin' it loud and proud!
Show 'em your
Verbalism Club spirit!
Do it for the children!
Do it for the sake
of your countrymen!
Do it for the world!
Our prayers are with you all!
That's right!
Come on! I believe!
[CHINOSUKE] Win it in loving
memory of your fallen comrade.
Show us your strength, Akira.
Be a hero, m'boy! Remember
who you've always been!
Right.
Who knew voices could
be so overwhelming?
Today, you're a man. Subete.
Thank you.
I believe in you. You can do it.
That's right. Never
forget you are our son.
I won't mom. I'm the
best of you both!
[VOICES shouting]
Intolerable human voices,
foolishly creating hope.
This cannot be!
[AKIRA]
To the Great Beyond!
[SUBETE]
Shred the stars!
Wield the sword of heaven!
No! Unacceptable!
[AKIRA, MAIA, SUBETE]
Universe Blade!
[M.J.B.K. A]
Su... be... te...?
[NESTA gasping]
[NESTA]
Kiryu.
[KIRYU]
My letter? Did you not read it?
It was atrocious!
[KIRYU] "These may well be the
last words of mine to reach you.
If only I had more time.
Tomorrow I face execution.
But be that as it may,
I have no regrets about
what brought me here.
For what little time
we had together,
I count myself
unimaginably fortunate.
My dying breath
will carry your name.
Your face will be the
last imagine in my mind.
Dying does not frighten
me because I am blessed
to leave this world with
my soul full of love."
[NESTA gasping]
[NESTA]
These aren't words of hate.
They're a declaration
of undying devotion!
How could I have let myself
believe otherwise?
[KIRYU]
I love you, Nesta.
[NESTA]
Kiryu!
[CROWD cheering]
So, uh, they won, right?
Far as I can tell.
[SHOKO] Then why are there kanji
on everything all of a sudden?
[SAKURAKO]
I can on only speculate,
but it's likely a side effect
of the Logos World
having disappeared.
[KOKONE]
The Logos World did this?
[KARAN]
That's how Aquarion is able
to be in our world
right now, isn't it?
[SAKURAKO]
Exactly.
Think of the kanji as refugees
from the Logos World's collapse.
The only way they can
sustain themselves
is by clinging to the
phenomena they represent.
[KENTO]
That can't be good.
[HAYATO]
I see. You're saying,
if written words have taken
concrete form in our world,
we can inadvertently give them
power by saying them aloud?
[KOKONE] S-So, you mean everyone
has V-Verbalism Ability now?
[SAKURAKO]
That's about the size of it.
[MAN A] You gonna give me my
money, or do I gotta get mean?
Y-You can die for all I care.
Huh?
[MAN A screaming]
[MAN B whimpering]
[SAKURAKO]
With the Logos World gone,
the World of Truth is
accessible to all mankind.
Am I ever gonna get a break?
[PEOPLE screaming]
[SAKURAKO]
Trouble is, as a culture,
for centuries we've only dealt
with Truth in the abstract.
We think in language.
We can't process
reality in the raw.
[KARAN]
Then, you mean...?
[SAKURAKO] I'm afraid so.
We're not out of the woods yet.
I hate to say it, but humanity
needs the Logos World.
That settles it.
Aquarion and I will merge.
And together form
a Logos of our own.
[AKIRA, SUBETE gasp]
The original was born
of Nesta's hatred.
But if I can merge
with love in my heart,
then in stands to reason
I can create a new one.
A Logos World founded
on compassion.
Maia.
Akira. I'm so grateful to you.
I'm just a puppet, but even
with Nesta gone I still exist.
That has to be your doing.
I have feelings for you.
Those feelings
made me human.
When I become the Logos World,
the human part of me will
most likely vanish altogether.
But that's okay. I'm satisfied.
[AKIRA]
You're an idiot.
Huh?!
I said you're an idiot.
I heard what you said, thanks.
Jeez, of all the times
to sling insults!
I made a promise to save you
and this world, remember?
You're not gonna
sacrifice yourself.
Then how are we supposed--
Let me do it.
I'll become the new Logos World.
[MAIA gasps]
[SUBETE] Hold on!
Who said you get to decide?
Subete?
Oh yeah, you'd love saving
the world, wouldn't you?
Screw that! I'll be
the hero for once!
Huh?!
[SUBETE] You're not
makin' this sacrifice!
I'll become the Logos World!
Then you'll know
the taste of defeat!
[AKIRA]
Shut up, rich kid.
[SUBETE]
Try 'n stop me, freak!
[AKIRA]
Loser.
[SUBETE]
Egotist.
[AKIRA]
Coward.
[SUBETE]
Block head!
[AKIRA]
Better than bein' a flake.
Guys, what are you doing?
Stop fighting over me!
[BOTH]
This isn't about you!
[MAIA]
Huh?
Shall we?
Don't see why not.
[MAIA]
Wha--? Hey, wait!
[yelling]
[TSUTOMU] Shouldn't it
technically be impossible
to win the last
battle without me?
How you gonna protect the world?
[KOKONE]
W-We'll be fine.
[KARAN]
Of course we will, silly!
[HAYATO]
Because we're believers!
[TSUTOMU] You're all working
together without me!
[AKIRA] I can protect the
world because I am not alone.
For I am...
[MAIA]
Go on.
[AKIRA]
You gotta be patient.
Final episode next.
[GROUP] "It Will Not End!
Aquarion Logos."