[MALE NEWSCASTER 22A]
We take you now live
to the press conference
being held in response
to the recent attacks by
what eyewitnesses describe
as giant robots.
[IWAGAMI]
Correct.
As of now, all fingers
point to DEAVA.
We know they possess weapons
similar to the ones used.
They've been on our terrorist
watch list for quite some time.
In addition to these to large,
mechanized objects,
jet-like fighter craft
was seen launching
from their Asagaya base.
Based on this, we have
to assume the organization
has access to an arsenal
of unprecedented proportions.
No longer can we allow
them to operate unchecked.
[beep]
Oh, well--I suppose we
can always sue for slander.
This doesn't bode well.
The Chief Secretary's
always been a supporter.
For him to pull a
180 like this
can only mean the poor bastard's
being manipulated by Nesta.
Yep.
Things are looking
pretty grim for us.
One might even say
downright hopeless.
[SOLDIER 22A]
No luck. It won't open.
[SAKAMOTO]
The hell you think that means?
[SOLDIER 22A]
I'm not sure, sir.
If I had to guess,
I'd say it's been sealed
by some kind of occult force.
[HAYATO] A defense system
based on Verbalism?
Exactly.
Turns out it's quite
an effective way
to reinforce locks.
If all they're trying
to get in with
is garden variety SWAT gear,
we've got at least
a couple of days.
So we're keeping
them out with a hybrid
of modern tech
and archaic magic?
That's my end of the
inventory, by the way.
Everything seems to match
what's on my list.
About to wrap up myself.
If we're lucky,
we'll have enough supplies
to last maybe a week.
[FEMALE NEWSCASTER 22A] For
those of you just joining us,
we've received confirmation
by government officials
that DEAVA is being held
responsible
for the many bizarre,
and in some cases, deadly,
occurrences over
the past few months.
Though a clear motive for the
terrorist group's activities
has yet to be established,
it's suspected that an
alarming number of teenagers
are among those recruited.
[gasps]
Hey, look!
[FEMALE OPERATOR 1A]
They've already got a list out?
[FEMALE OPERATOR 1B]
We look like criminals!
This is nuts!
What are we supposed do?
[KENTO]
Here. This one's for you.
I'm not hungry.
Sweetie, I know
you're hurtin', but...
[door opens, closes]
[KOKONE]
C'mon.
You've g-got to eat s-something.
We didn't just
lose Maia out there.
We also l-lost Tsutomu.
I'll... I'll just leave this.
Akira, p-please.
There's got to be
s-something I can do to help.
How can I g-give you strength?
Look, I'm not worth
the effort, okay?
[KOKONE gasps]
I can't.
I don't have it in me.
I'm not a savior.
In the end, all I did was
make things even worse for him.
I made him suffer.
Wait... Wait a sec...
Him who?
What the hell?!
I can't remember!
Heh... whatever. Guess he
can't be that important.
[NESTA] Letting him
slip your mind, I see.
[NESTA giggles]
Ah, well.
I suppose puppets aren't
known for their memories.
I remember you.
Your name is Nesta.
What exactly do you
want from me?
That, my precocious
little vessel,
I can sum up quite easily.
I wish to see
this civilization dead.
Using Aquarion Logos.
[SUBETE]
Impressive machine, isn't it?
[HAYASHI]
Yes.
To say your own
doesn't quite measure up
would be a bold understatement.
The good news is this adds
two remote-controlled Vectors
to the mix, when and if you'll
be able to Merge with them.
[SUBETE]
And when might that be?
[HAYASHI]
I don't like being rushed.
And at any rate you need
adequate time to recover.
[SUBETE]
What are you implying?
[HAYASHI] You imagine
I'm blissfully unaware
of your health issues?
When the People of Truth
were pushed
to the brink of extinction
by the People of Writing,
they needed something
to turn the tide of battle
in their favor.
What they found,
for want of a better word,
was Kiryu's corpse.
With it, they created
the Book of Verbalism.
Since you're the clear
heir to Kiryu's power,
it's understood that
your body can be used
to the same effect as the book.
But, the human organism
can only sustain
that kind of power for so long.
Heh. Nothing gets by you,
does it?
[HAYASHI] Is quitting while
you're ahead not an option?
[SUBETE]
Hardly.
Not when I've yet to deal
Kaibuki the final blow.
My identity depends
on defeating him.
[HAYASHI]
Sounds like a fixation.
I spent my entire life
looking to Father.
I wanted to be noticed.
I chased after something
I could never have.
Just when I was on
the verge of discovering
who the man really was,
he perished right
before my eyes.
I hold Akira Kaibuki
responsible for his death.
[SUBETE] I've come to
accept that I'm not someone
who's able to stand
on his own two feet.
With nothing else
to cling to, I'm a nonentity.
Revenge is the only
thing I have left.
[HAYATO] How long
do you plan on sulking?
Look,
I know we've been through a lot,
but bowing out isn't
going to solve this.
We have to get the politicians
out of Nesta's control.
Vector Ga is our only strategy.
[HAYATO] Akira.
We need you on this. Please!
Sorry, but...
I'm not your guy.
[HAYATO growls]
That's enough!
Tsutomu didn't die
so you could sit around
feeling sorry for yourself!
No one else can do what you do!
You're all we have, damn it!
Look me in the eye!
Aren't you The Savior?
Not anymore, I'm not.
Sorry to disappoint you.
[KOKONE gasps]
We're all grieving,
but what happened with Tsutomu
and Vector Ga wasn't your fault.
You have to understand that!
Would you leave me alone?
I'm not...
I'm not The Savior, okay?
[slap]
[KOKONE gasps]
I'm s-sorry, I... I didn't...
This is our fault
for putting too much
of the burden on your shoulders.
I am so sorry.
[HAYATO]
Akira...
[KOKONE panting]
[KOKONE]
Wh-What's wrong with me?
He's in p-pain and I t-tried
to g-guilt him over it...
[KOKONE gasps]
Wait, who...?
Who was I talking about?
[SAKURAKO]
This may be for the best.
If there's any substance
to what Maia was saying,
he really shouldn't
be piloting Vector Ga.
I'm not sure I follow.
It's too dangerous for him.
Hang on...
Uh... Too dangerous for who?
Well, there's no point
in me being here anymore.
[SUBETE]
A concept disappears.
When the word for Akira
vanishes altogether,
not even your closet allies
will register your existence.
But I will.
Since I am now in
possession of the Book,
the concept of that word
will never be lost to me.
Akira.
Even if no one else in the world
remembers that you
ever existed at all,
part of you will live on
inside of me forever.
This is why I win.
I shall push you to the brink...
...and beyond!
Verbalize and rejoice!
For today I set you free!
[screeching noise]
[M.J.B.K. vocalizes]
[CROWD gasps, murmurs]
[HAYATO]
Fantastic.
[KENTO]
This shouldn't be happening.
The base has its own
emergency generator.
This isn't just a power outage.
[NESTA]
Electricity is the lifeblood
of modern civilization.
Releasing an M.J.B.K. that
will wipe the very concept
from existence?
How ruthless.
[SUBETE] What did Maia say
when you saw her last?
I could hardly bear
to be in her company.
[giggles]
Poor doll's wracked by the agony
of her failed attempts
to play Pinocchio.
She wants so badly to be human.
Why not erase
it all from her mind?
You do have it in you
to show her that mercy.
[pounding noise]
It's about time.
All right, we're going in!
[snap]
Not even batteries
are functional.
Electricity is gone.
It's just stopped flowing.
[KENTO]
Bad news, ma'am.
They've busted through
the back door of the café.
What? Already?
We knew it was
only a matter of time
before they
made it inside.
Of course we have the M.J.B.K.
to deal with now, too.
Are--Are the Vectors
still functional?
They operate on Verbalism, so
the outage won't affect them.
Trouble is, without electricity,
we can't get 'em
off the launchpads.
I say we get inside 'em,
shoot through the walls,
and high-tail it out
of this pop-stand!
That's not possible.
They can navigate
without electricity,
but the firing
mechanism won't work.
Any other ideas?
[gunfire, groaning]
[SAKAMOTO] Keep moving!
They're just past here!
Stay sharp!
[SAKURAKO] We could
crawl through the ducts
at the end of
the elevator shaft.
We just have to hope
it doesn't occur to them
to look for us there.
I want the three
of you to get out of here.
Be as stealthy as possible.
Commander, we're
in this together!
The worst conceivable outcome
is that we lose you kids,
do you understand me?
We can't risk it!
There'd be no one
to fight the M.J.B.K!
But the Vectors...!
[SAKURAKO]
Don't worry.
They won't get them
without a fight.
And if they're commandeered,
there's always a chance
to get them back.
Our priority is
keeping you safe.
Without you, the Vectors
are scrap anyway.
Now quit arguing
and move it!
So wait, we don't
get a say in this?
No. you don't.
Sorry to be harsh.
[HAYATO]
Come on.
[KARAN yelps]
But... Big Brother!
[HAYATO]
Kikogami.
[KENTO]
Shoko. You should go with them.
But I hafta...
[OFFICER 22A]
What the hell's going on?
I'm talking to you!
Oh, crap!
[OFFICER 22A]
Hold it!
[MAN 22A]
Somebody! Help!
[MAN 22B]
What happened to him?
[MAN 22C]
Are you okay, sir?
[MAN 22D]
We should get him to a hospital.
[MAN 22A] There's a clinic
two blocks north of here.
[FEMALE VOICE 22A]
Help!
[FEMALE VOICE 22B]
Someone! Please!
[MAN, WOMAN screaming]
[KOKONE panting]
How did I m-manage
to l-lose the others?
You're one of those terrorists!
Yeah! I read
all about it online!
[KOKONE]
N-No, it's--
Where you think you're going?
[KOKONE gasps]
Look out!
[HAYATO] Damn it. I can't
get through to Kikogami.
This doesn't make sense.
The Aquariphone works
without electricity.
Why the hell
isn't she answering?
[KARAN sobbing]
[HAYATO]
Karan?
I... I don't get it.
I mean, we've been
fighting to protect people
this whole time, haven't we?
We're the good guys.
Why's everyone
treating us like crap?
I thought heroes are supposed
to be treated like heroes!
[HAYATO]
I don't know, sweetie.
Apparently good deeds don't
guarantee you a smooth ride.
The world's a
topsy-turvy place, huh?
[OFFICER 22B]
There they are!
[OFFICER 22C]
Over here! This way!
[OFFICER 22D]
Circle around the back!
[KIDS crying]
[KOKONE]
You kids okay?
S-Somebody!
We need help! Please!
Can anyone hear me?
We've f-fallen into a sinkhole!
P-Please! Anybody!
We're down here!
Sorry. I d-don't think
anyone can hear me.
[KOUNOSUKE]
You're like a stray dog.
[AKIRA]
Grandpa?
[SHIZUKA] I'll have you know
we've been worried sick.
[AKIRA]
Yeah, I'm sorry.
[KOUNOSUKE]
Try writing it.
[FEMALE ONLOOKER 22A] They're
calling them terrorists now.
[MALE ONLOOKER 22B] How many
innocent people have died
because of you, huh?
[MALE ONLOOKER 22C] Got nothing
to say for yourselves,
murderers?
[HAYATO]
Shut up!
[OFFICER 22E]
Hey. Knock it off.
[HAYATO] Listen,
I get that you're scared.
But you can't take it out
on the first target
they put in front of you.
It doesn't solve
thing for anyone.
At least look at the facts
before you lash out.
Do you really
think human beings
could be responsible
for all this devastation?
Form you own opinions
for once in your lives!
Does this little girl strike
you as a cold-blooded killer?
Save it for the firing squad.
I'll shout it 'til my throat
is raw if I have to!
We're here to
protect all of you!
[KOKONE gasps]
H-Hayato. Is that you?
I'm down here!
But... His voice...
I heard it.
It r-reached me, clear as day.
How is that possible?
[KOKONE] Maybe in the right
place at the right time,
words spoken sincerely
from the heart
hold a special power.
What does my heart say?
Right here, right now?
[KOKONE gasps]
[KOKONE sings in Japanese]
[singing continues]
[SHIZUKA]
Akira...
[KOUNOSUKE]
Has it really been seven years?
I remember taking
you off the streets
like it was yesterday.
I'll never forget what you
told us in the beginning:
Without a hint of irony, you
said you'd become The Savior.
Those words are your essence,
the very foundation
of who you are.
I remember.
[singing continues]
[KOKONE]
My voice will reach him!
I know it!
[singing continues]
[SHIZUKA]
What's wrong, dear?
[AKIRA]
Can't you hear it?
She needs me.
[singing continues]
[SHIZUKA chuckles]
[KOUNOSUKE chuckles]
Release them at once.
That's an order.
[OFFICER 22D]
Senator Kobayakawa?
I don't understand.
I've come here on
official government business.
The so-called
terrorists are innocent.
[OFFICER 22D]
But sir...
--[OFFICER 22D grunts]
--[OFFICER 22F groans]
[HAYATO]
What is this?
What's going on?
When the truth fails
to move people as you wish,
distasteful as it may be,
coercion works.
[KARAN]
Mom! Tinoa!
[SHOKO]
Everyone stay where you are!
Try anything and I'll
trigger the ship's
self-destruct mechanism!
[SAKURAKO]
What are you doing?
Wait, Shoko?
[SHOKO] There's nothing
left for me anymore.
Why not just end it?
[SHOKO]
This is...
[TSUTOMU] I wonder...
Was I able to make Shoko smile?
[TSUTOMU] Now why you gotta
go and make my woman cry?
[TSUTOMU] Seriously.
Girl's got a fantastic one.
I love it.
[SHOKO]
His voice!
[SHOKO crying]
[SHOKO]
No! I have to smile!
Tsutomu died bringing
happiness back!
I owe it to him to go on,
to smile every chance I get!
[AKIRA panting]
[KOKONE singing]
[AKIRA grunts]
You really heard me!
Akira?
[AKIRA]
You needed me, so I came.
As long as I
can hear your voice,
or the voices of those
in trouble, I'll be there.
[AKIRA]
For I am The Sav--
[KOKONE]
When Maia disappeared,
my first thought was,
"This is my chance."
I guess I w-wanted
her out of the picture,
so you and I could be a thing.
B-But I totally h-hated
myself for feeling that way.
What I love most
about you is the way...
The way you're
so s-straightforward
about what needs to be done.
Always.
So what now?
What do you need?
What'll help you be
who you want to be?
Who is it you
really want to save?
At the moment, it's Maia.
More than anything.
I thought so.
[AKIRA]
I have to go.
[SAKAMOTO]
Hold up, men. At ease.
Mr. Sakamoto?
What the heck
are you doing here?
[SAKAMOTO]
Shoko, I... I'm sorry.
I didn't realize you
still worked here.
[SHOKO] No. This is
clearly a message for me.
I need a favor, sir.
If you could...
Tell Senator Iwagami
his daughter
wants to see him immediately.
[KENTO gasps]
His what, now?
What were you like in
elementary school, Maia?
I trained intensely every day.
Of course. What about Subete?
I used to play with Maia
in our secret base.
I only agreed to it because
you were so damn pushy.
Was not!
You chowed down on my dirt
dumplings and mud cider!
So I'm guessing
you two were close?
[SUBETE]
Quite.
Next, Episode 23.
[MAIA] "Revive! The Vow
Beneath the Moonlight."
[KARAN]
I should've kept my mouth shut.