[GIRL A]
Ta-da!
Wow, it's a Marin Sparkling
Mode! Those are ultra-rare!
[GIRL C]
That's so cool!
Hey, congrats! That's awesome!
Yeah, right?
Oh, hey! Check it out!
That child-like
innocence is so refreshing.
Here, Tinoa, have a look.
I don't really care
'bout that kinda stuff.
Oh.
Mika, look at this! I got
a Marin Sparkling Mode!
[SHOKO]
A school festival performance?
Yes indeedy, sweetie!
Hayato's University
is hosting the festival.
And they've been gracious enough
to let the Verbalism Club
Reading Theatre troupe perform!
He goes to Seiso
University, doesn't he?
If I'm not mistaken, Seiso U
holds a big deal debate contest
every year during that festival.
Aren't any of the
boys working today?
[OURA sighs]
No beefcakes?!
[SAKURAKO]
Meow.
[KOKONE]
A-Akira's not here.
And n-neither are
the other guys.
If you're looking for Akira
or Hayato, they're gone.
Tsutomu took them
out for something
he referred to as a
"group blind date".
[gasps] A d-date?
[BOTH]
Oh god!
Uh... Don't go.
Retreating? We win.
No, we lost! Three strikes,
and they're out the door!
Ah, I'm screwed!
So much for findin' a
girlfriend in November
so our romance can blossom
into a Christmas miracle!
How boring.
I have better things to do
than to get dragged into this.
I'll remember that next time.
Things only got weird when you
opened your big, stupid mouth.
Aren't my nails,
like, totes cute?
They're not.
Decorating your fingers with
cooked eels is disconcerting.
Don't ruin this for me.
She asked for my opinion,
which I gave her.
And I'm tellin' ya,
that's not how it works.
You gotta be Mister Compliments,
even when it's a lie.
Smile and say,
"looks nice", got it?
Just lie? I could never do that.
[RANKO]
What more is there to say?
My daughter's potential
to become the mascot
for My Storm is obvious.
I've heard the same spiel before
from innumerable parents.
A lot of it depends on
how eager Karan here is
to join this project.
I really wanna do it!
Is that so?
Ugh! I was lying, obviously!
I don't wanna do it,
I don't wanna!
[RANKO] Karan, mind
your manners, young lady.
I don't like that guy.
He looks at me weird.
[RANKO] This weekend
you have a performance
with the Verbalism Club.
Oh, during Seiso
University's festival?
How nice!
The perfect opportunity to
make a good first impression
with some future elites.
I guess.
A friend of yours?
Sorta, we're in the same class.
But we've never really
talked with each other much.
There's not a lotta trash,
we could say we emptied it,
and no one would even know.
Good idea!
[KARAN]
Tinoa!
[TINOA]
Huh?
What's up?
Hey, are you free this weekend?
You wanna go to Seiso
University's school festival
with me?
I'm part of a reading
theater troupe.
It would be great if you could
come and watch me perform.
Why me?
[KARAN]
Hmm. Well, I guess...
The thing is, you seem cool,
Tinoa. I think I might like you.
[TINOA]
Huh?
I mean it!
Karan, it's time to go.
'Kay, wait just a sec!
[KARAN]
Here's my card.
[TINOA]
Oh...
See you Sunday!
Yeah, but... I don't
have a cellphone.
[HAYATO] "No! It can't be
true. That's impossible.
You killed my father,
and you're a girl!"
"I am your father post-op!"
[HAYATO]
"I've searched my feelings.
I know them to be true,
but this is still a lot
of information to process
mid-saber fight, dad."
"Stop right there!"
Umm, A-Akira?
You're just a Strawtrooper,
you're not supposed
to draw focus.
"May the Force of
Suction be with you!"
No Tinoa.
[MAIA]
Oh, yummy!
I never thought eating
a Shirobaco lunch box
out in nature could be
so absolutely perfect!
This must be what
they call a picnic!
Cute, but crazy.
Ain't it always the way?
[TINOA]
Excuse me.
I was wondering if
you'd seen someone?
Some who?
Well, she's got bright
colored twin tails
and she's shorter than me
and has real big eyes.
Twin tails. Big eyes.
[MONSTER wailing]
I know of no monster
fitting that description.
No? Okay.
[STUDENT A] The debate
competition is starting soon!
[STUDENT B]
Let's hurry!
[STUDENT C]
Hey, look over there.
Mister Econ and Poli Sci major.
[STUDENT D]
Whoa, what a total hottie.
[STUDENT C]
And he got the top score
on his entrance exam.
He's so perfect. Think
he has a girlfriend?
Good afternoon, and
welcome to Seiso University.
The debate contest
will begin shortly.
As always, the
competition follows
an elimination
tournament format.
This year, the winner will also
get to have an exhibition debate
with our special guest, rising
star of the political world,
Masatsugu Kobayakawa.
Kobayakawa?
Now then, without
further ado, let's debate!
Contestants, please!
[applause]
What is he doing here?
[FACILITATOR] Participating
in extemporaneous debate,
Akira Kaibuki!
And his theme:
"On the Merits of a Savior".
[AKIRA]
The issue's not up for debate.
Because I...
...am the Savior!
[FACILITATOR] Does that
complete your argument?
Indeed.
That moron.
[MAIA]
You hungry?
Not really.
[MAIA]
Eat some.
No, I'm fine.
[MAIA]
I said eat!
[applause]
Big Bro Hayato, you can do it!
[OURA, OKAZAKI]
Hayato!
[HAYATO]
As citizens of our nation,
we must each think of ways
to improve the economy.
[HAYATO] I'm going to show
you a series of charts.
in this first one, we divided
the national debt by the numb...
Next slide. Please
note the contrast.
Compare the GDP figures
from before the war
to those of present day.
This concludes my proposal for
substantial economic reform.
[applause]
Yuuto Horishima, you're up next.
If you have a counter
proposal, please proceed.
You wanna hear the
most effective policy
for our economy?
Then bam!
Reduce the consumption tax
to zero percent, broseph!
[HAYATO]
Uh!
I'm afraid the issue
isn't quite that simple.
Why not?
Lowering prices will just
give people the incentive
to buy more!
So bam! Zero percent!
We're Generation Zero!
[CROWD cheering]
[STUDENT H]
Hey, Horishima's at it again!
[STUDENT E]
Seriously? Let's check it out!
Our school's debate competition
has certainly changed
since it began.
Now it's nothing more than a
rambling popularity contest.
From what I've seen,
that sort of thing's all the
younger generation cares about.
[HAYATO]
I see.
I can't blame the others
for not sticking around.
I think you did great in there.
You proved your point
to me, at least.
As opposed to that fart-brained
"zero percent" guy.
But he was able to
captivate the audience.
Seldom are the masses interested
in someone who's right.
Like my father, the senator,
a simply terrible orator.
[KARAN]
Huh?
[HAYATO]
Lying went against his nature,
so he never exaggerated.
Straight to the point,
not entertaining.
"His speeches could cure
insomnia", they used to say.
It was a sentiment shared
by most of his peers.
I used to look down
on my father for that,
but then something happened.
Oh yeah? What?
[HAYATO]
You really want to hear?
When I was in middle school,
cheating on tests was
rampant among my friends.
No one had any problem
with letting the other kids
look over their answers.
Except me. I wasn't comfortable
following that trend
and I refused to
lie to the teacher.
When I let him know
what was happening,
several of them were suspended.
Naturally, that would make
facing them difficult.
So I left,
transferred to a new school
before their suspension was up.
But why? You didn't
do anything wrong.
I know.
But to those who were punished,
my righteousness made
me their bad guy.
But I couldn't choose
any other path in life.
At this rate,
I'll never be a force for
political change in Japan.
I'm afraid my goal
was just a pipedream.
That's not true.
[SUBETE]
The words are in pain.
People's karma,
accumulating into culture.
Then all the more reason
you must free them, Subete.
Don't you think?
Verbalize and rejoice, for
today I deign to set you free.
[M.J.B.K. howling]
[alarms beeping]
M.J.B.K. alert.
Yeah, but look.
Do you see anything
weird happening?
[HAYASHI]
You're pushing it too hard.
Even if you can
handle the strain,
your machine is
going to break down.
[SUBETE] It only needs to
hold out a little longer.
When will you have it fixed?
[HAYASHI]
I'd like to have two weeks.
[SUBETE]
Very well.
Isn't it in the
realm of possibility
that our M.J.B.K. friend
currently on the rampage
could defeat your enemy for you?
If it happens, it happens.
[AKIRA]
Genesis Merge. Shout it!
[BOTH]
Aquarion!
[AKIRA, MAIA]
San!
So far so good. Akira seems
to be handling that baby
without any
problems at all.
Let's all hope
it stays that way.
Word corrosion rate
is on the rise.
Something's wrong.
[PRESIDENT]
Whaddaya think?
A huge idea to help
sell our new concept.
Cutting edge stuff, sir.
The most outside-the-box idea
I've seen in my whole career.
[GIRL D]
You like it?
Lookin' good. That
style suits you.
[GIRL F]
Like, model sexy.
Do I have what it
takes to go pro?
Oh, yeah! Definitely!
[TSUTOMU] Wait, did the M.J.B.K.
make things more peaceful?
There're fewer arguments
with each passing minute.
All these white lies have
eliminated personal conflicts.
So maybe this M.J.B.K.
isn't all that bad?
There's still a danger,
don't be fooled.
It's here.
I sense you!
Did I get it?
[AKIRA]
No, it was a fake.
[M.J.B.K.]
Uso! Uso! Uso!
Uso!
[MAIA sighs]
This fog is too thick. I can't
discern its actual shape.
A fog of lies.
Akira and Maia are up
there fighting it already.
Then we'd better hurry up!
I'm such a dog-face,
there's no freaking way
I'm ever winning this.
That's not true at all, Yuuko.
You're easily the
cutest girl here.
No matter who wins,
let's all stay friends!
[DUDE] La! La! La la la!
Goalie! Goalie!
Saying random words while
flailing wildly is hilarious.
Way funny.
[KARAN]
Uh.
What is it?
[CROWD laughing]
The laughing... it's creepy.
[beeping]
[SHOKO] We've got a problem
with the word corrosion rate!
It's rising rapidly,
and your University seems
to be at the epicenter.
[KOBAYAKAWA]
We're currently experiencing
an economic downturn
with no end in sight.
Full time jobs are drying up.
I'm sure many of you
current University students
must have growing concerns
about finding employment
when you graduate.
But burying your head in the
sand will never change anything.
It is at trying
times like these
when we most need to join hands.
Let's reach for a
better tomorrow
by forging bonds
between us today.
Then we'll reach that utopia
of equality and happiness.
Oh wow, I have no retort.
You are really
something, Senator.
[SHOKO] Videos of the Senator's
speech are spreading quickly,
which seems to be
directly linked
to the rise in word corrosion.
It shows no sign of stopping!
I know him. He's a politician
named Kobayakawa.
He's called the "young
hope of the ruling party."
Why would a young politician's
speech raise the corrosion rate?
[HAYATO]
Uncertainty reigns over us all.
Whaddaya mean, Big Bro?
Opinions can be tricky things
because opinions can always
be rejected by others.
And thinking for yourself?
Why bother if you can
let someone else?
[HAYATO]
If you're afraid of being hurt,
you can live surrounded
by pleasant-sounding lies.
Giving yourself over
to a big lie is simple
and seems like a
happy way to live.
[KARAN]
But it's not.
[HAYATO]
Yeah, I know that much.
But that's the life
too many citizens choose.
If the masses want to be
caught up in the current,
the proper move for a politician
is to lead them down
the path they've chosen.
But I can't in good conscience.
[MAN A]
What's your problem, runt?
[KARAN]
Tinoa.
[TINOA] Apologize!
You broke it, say sorry.
No, I'm telling you,
you're mistaken.
[TINOA]
I saw it happen!
Don't worry about it.
It's fine, okay?
[TINOA]
It's not fine!
Hey stop blaming our
princess, all right?
The lady who made it even
said everything's fine!
What's with this kid?
So, we're free to go, aren't we?
Of course.
[chuckles] It wasn't
anything special anyway.
Why are you smiling?
I saw 'em do it!
[ALL laughing]
[TINOA]
You looked so sad when it broke.
Stop lying to yourself!
[WOMAN A]
Shut up, you dumb brat!
[HAYATO]
I understand.
No matter what other people say,
there are some things you
just can't back down from.
You're so awkward that living
honestly is the only way.
Never forget... there are
other kids like you, too.
[MAIA]
What now?
It's quite simple.
We just have to clear
out this fog of lies.
But how?
The people's will...
must be restored.
[KOBAYAKAWA]
I will say it once again.
Keep believing! Have faith!
Your future is bright!
[thud]
No, Kobayakawa.
Everything you say
is a candy-coated lie!
Lie? About what?
Come on, it's this way.
[HAYATO] You spoke of a utopia
of happiness and equality.
But are you and I equal?
Absolutely not.
You were born into a family
that's been in politics
for generations.
You were virtually
guaranteed success
from the moment you were born.
Athletic ability,
intelligence, personality.
Every single one of us was born
with unique characteristics.
It's one of those things we all
learn when we're still young.
No two people are exactly alike.
And if that's the truth,
how can we all be equal?
In spite of these facts,
people still delude themselves
with the sweet lie
of equality, and why?
Because they refuse to
recognize their own inferiority
in the grand scheme.
Instead, they cling to
the false comfort of a lie.
Your pessimistic line of
thought underestimates people.
Indeed, it is true there
are differences between us,
but those differences
give more meaning to us
walking hand in hand.
Pretty words, but hollow.
"Hand in hand," then what?
We form these bonds,
but to what end?
Without thinking further ahead,
the very means you suggested
have devolved into
their own end.
What meaning could be
found in that existence?
What's truly necessary
is for us all
to exercise critical thought.
Without that, you brandish
the idea of connections,
but betray their meaning.
Such knee-jerk abandonment
of critical thinking
will lead to a society
of brain-dead zombies.
Who's this jerk?
He's pissin' me off.
How lame.
You need to have more
faith in your fellow man.
Believe in the
potential of people.
Faith alone will change nothing.
Why bother connecting with
others if it leads to a society
where you have to just
accept how things are?
Where you have to
lie about yourself
if you hope to
fit in with others?
And where you
ostracize the people
who aren't callow
enough to live a lie.
[HAYATO]
Dishonesty has become
an almost necessary
societal lubricant.
But no more.
I reject that notion.
I choose not accept your lies!
I choose the more
difficult path!
I choose the path of honesty!
The sad truth is honest people
are seen as weaklings, fools.
However, there are outsiders
who will never cling to lies,
no matter how much
they might suffer!
Those are the people
I'm speaking to now.
Even though you know
the truth can never win
against the ocean of lies,
there's a fool here who
will stand against it,
fighting all of
their glib posturing.
And I am that fool!
You awkward, honest people,
know that you're not alone.
What's her deal? Acting
like she's so great.
Lame little goody two shoes.
I'm not alone. I'm...
I'm here for you.
Wha--? What is wrong with you?
[SHOKO] Word corrosion rate
is slowly starting to drop!
[MAIA]
The mist is clearing.
[AKIRA] The fog of lies
pouring from its mouth
hid the truth from view.
Now then.
[M.J.B.K. groaning]
[AKIRA]
I will take these away.
[AKIRA] The empty fog
of lies is dissipating.
And with your fangs removed...
...you're no more
than a paper tiger.
[AKIRA]
Burst Through!
[MAIA yelling]
[M.J.B.K.]
Uso!
[HAYATO]
Heh. This won't change anything.
But, someday, I'll fix
this damaged world
while staying true
to my awkward self.
[KARAN] Saying you want to
do things you don't want to
and saying you like
things you don't like.
I hate it, but lies like
that are part of my life.
But that's showbiz.
I understand.
I'm gonna have to live with lies
from this point on, ya know?
All for my dream.
It's just,
I think being able to live
the way you do is wonderful.
I respect it.
And I get it now.
I know why I kept thinking
about you, Tinoa.
So whaddaya say, do you
wanna be... friends?
No thanks.
[KARAN]
Uh.
[sighs]
[AKIRA]
We're heading back.
Right.
[gasps]
[MAIA] Kokone Kikogami,
I saw an extraterrestrial!
It had four legs and a cedar
tree growing from its back!
[KOKONE]
That's no ET.
[SUBETE]
No, Maia!
That's just a fairy from
Suginami-saurus Island!
[MAIA]
A what now?
[SUBETE] Dad told me good
fortune comes to those
who can catch it!
[MAIA]
We have to catch one, Kikogami!
[KOKONE]
Actually, that's Namisuke.
[SUBETE]
Next: Episode 19.
[KOKONE]
"Fall in Love! Asagaya."