Don't be shy.
Show yourself, M.J.B.K.
[M.J.B.K. A]
Dan! Dan! Dan! Da-Dan!
[MAIA] Where'd these guys
come from? What's going on?
[M.J.B.K. A]
Da-Dan!
Man, my network sucks!
Just connect already!
[HAYATO] It's causing a wide
scale communications breakdown,
which could deal the deathblow
to society as we know it.
[MAIA] It has the power
to sever connections?
And it's strong enough
to prevent our Merge.
[AKIRA] Real bonds can't
be cut that easily.
Those that tie us
together are stronger.
[MAIA]
Kaibuki.
C'mon.
We can do this!
Genesis Merge! Shout it!
[BOTH]
Aquarion!
[AKIRA, MAIA]
Moonbind!
[M.J.B.K. A]
Dan! Dan! Dan!
After years of waiting,
the voice has come.
Through the surging power
of the "bond" kanji,
people and information that
wouldn't normally be connected
are now intrinsically linked.
Uh. What's going on?
There's data flowing
in from hundreds,
no, thousands of sources.
Far out.
Lame! My stupid parents are
totally coming down on me
for like no reason.
My folks're sweatin' me, too.
[SALARYMAN]
Huh?
This place.
[MAIA gasps]
[MAIA]
Master Sougon!
[AKIRA]
That's him.
With the rising tide
of ultimate connection,
people will bind each
other in chains of hate.
Thus, the world
will consume itself.
And become the basis
for a new M.J.B.K.
Verbalize and rejoice.
For today, I set you free!
Master Sougon!
[SUBETE]
All right.
It's up to me to bring
Maia back safely.
Hayashi?
I altered the design.
And honestly the logic
was an absolute mess.
I'd have to give this
design a failing grade.
Ha. Though the concept
is rather intriguing.
[SUBETE]
Then...
[HAYASHI] I tuned and
calibrated her myself.
After installing the
new system, of course.
She's in the hangar,
waiting for you.
Thank you.
Master Sougon, why won't you
say anything? What's wrong?
[AKIRA]
It's coming. Eyes forward.
[M.J.B.K. B] En. En. En. En.
En. En. En. En. En. En. En. En!
Ooh. Th-That sucks.
[phone ringing]
Hayato here.
[HATANO] It's Hatano.
I'm calling from the office.
Somehow, Karan's video
was sent from my account.
Now thousands of people
are responding negatively.
I need you to make it go away!
[HATANO] We've got to
do something, Kujyo.
[M.J.B.K. B]
En. En. En. En. En!
[HAYATO]
Buckle up.
This is a literal flame war.
It's my time. After all,
I am the Chosen One.
Verbalize!
[SOUGON]
In times past,
humanity was at one
with the world of truth.
But the written word,
for all we prospered from it,
wrought incalculable suffering.
[SHOKO] The video has already
been uploaded to multiple sites
and it's sending itself out
across all social
media platforms.
[KENTO] So, does that mean
it's being forced on people
who don't even wanna watch it?
What the hell? I didn't
do any of that!
I just uploaded the damn thing
to the same site I always use!
Never read the comments.
[BROTHER A] Lookit this,
big bro! That guy has Chappy!
[BROTHER B]
Huh? Lemme see! It is her!
That skunk head comic
stole some poor kid's dog?
He's like, worser than Stalin.
[BOY A]
Let's repost the link.
[BOY B]
We're such good people.
[TSUTOMU]
That's a load of crap!
How'd I go from net
comedian to dog napper?
I borrowed that mutt
from a buddy of mine!
I know, look.
The dog in Tsutomu's video and
the one in the owner's picture
have completely
different collars.
Also their eyes and
fur colors don't match.
[KOKONE]
Y-You're right.
[HAYATO] They look alike,
but these are different dogs.
And now I'm bein' hung out
to dry 'cause of this B.S.!
That M.J.B.K. is toast!
I'll come with.
Prepare for launch.
[SOUGON] People will always
see what they want to see.
Believe what they
want to believe.
[NEWSCASTER A] Earlier today,
a decision was made
not to indict former
cabinet minister Akasaka,
who was under investigation
for the embezzlement
of public funds.
A press conference was held
after the announcement.
[COMMENTATOR A]
With the indictment dropped,
further scrutiny will be
directed at Senator Hatano,
the whistle blower in
this alleged scandal.
[GUY A]
Sir?
[HATANO]
Uh.
Wh-- That's a lie.
I never did any of this.
Who's spreading
this misinformation?
[SOUGON] What these sheep
yearn for is not the truth,
only that fleeting
moment of pleasure felt
when nipping at a person
like a pack of wolves.
Communication between
these simple minds
now spreads at
the speed of thought,
lowering the value
of their hurtful words
to the level of
their base character.
The fools disarm themselves.
[SHOKO]
Commander, you're here.
Glad to see you
all being proactive.
Let's get Kujyo and Domon
in the air, double time.
[MAIA] I'll tear you apart
with my bare hands!
That Vector!
We've got an
unidentified Vector.
Hang on. It's the same machine
that was in the initial attack.
That Vector...
[SUBETE] If I ever want
Maia restored to me,
I must first learn
to be worthy of her!
Subete, that's you, isn't it?
I can't get the comm system
to connect with Maia's machine.
Guess someone must've
messed around with the O.S.
No problem!
I'll take Maia back just as
soon as I've defeated you.
Got that, Red Vector?
Those maneuvers.
Is it really Subete?
M.J.B.K., listen to me.
Serve me! Merge with me!
I did it!
We'll wait and see.
[SUBETE]
Go! Flame attack!
[yelps]
[SHOKO] Cockpit temperature's
rising rapidly!
It's over the heat
resistance limit!
[SHOKO] You're in danger!
Get out of there!
[SHOKO] Are you both
all right? Please respond!
Kaibuki...
Th-This...
--[SHOKO] Reading 40% damage.
--This is bad.
Heat dispersal just
can't keep up!
So where are Kujyo and Domon?
[TSUTOMU] We're all
set to go. Let's boogie!
[SHOKO]
Sorry.
Bad news. The entire
area is too saturated.
If they were to deploy now,
their Vector's armor
would melt in roughly
point four eight seconds.
But Aquarion can handle
it though, right?
Why don't we launch
already Merged?
[SHOKO] Merging on this
plane is impossible.
Vectors only function
in the Logos World.
Do your homework.
[TSUTOMU]
Damn it!
Ridiculous.
That naïve upstart tried to
use me to further his career,
but in the end,
he only wasted my time.
[SECRETARY] It seems there's
some residual uproar online.
Leave them to it.
Besides, they're just a
bunch of talentless losers
full of hot air.
Mister Akasaka!
[HATANO]
Yes, I'm aware of the backlash.
We have no comment at this time.
Good lord! What's that?
[SOUGON]
Over 12 millennia have passed
since the written word
first came to be.
Humanity developed urban
civilization, a modern society,
but was blinded long ago
to the truth of this world.
Ever since this advancement,
people have relied on words,
while slowly fracturing them,
belittling them, or
applying false meanings.
Can the dawn of understanding
shed its light
on this self-inflicted darkness?
[PEOPLE yelling]
[WOMAN A]
Watch out!
[TSUTOMU] Isn't there
any way we can launch?
Whoa! The hell's that?
Another side effect
of the M.J.B.K.?
The malice of the
internet's bottom feeders
has manifested as dark flame.
[KOKONE gasps]
Tsu-Tsutomu?
[TSUTOMU yelps]
[TSUTOMU]
What's goin' on?
Hot! Hot!
[KOKONE]
He-Here we go!
Watch out!
[KARAN screams]
[KARAN]
Thank you, big bro!
Kento, assemble
emergency response!
[KENTO]
Aye, aye!
[SHOKO]
Commander!
Word corrosion rate
now exceeds 80%!
If we don't fix this,
the entire concept of
flame will be extinguished.
There has to be
something we've missed.
[SOUGON]
Further proving my point,
the village idiots mistakenly
believe they are safe
from the malignant venom
they endlessly vomit.
All too soon, they shall
learn how wrong they are.
They will learn that the
blade of the written word,
when pointed at another,
can cut both ways.
[YOUNG MAN] I hope you die.
Get rekt, you scrub!
Heh?
[YOUNG MAN screaming]
[MEN screaming]
Over here! Please!
No use! They won't go out!
Hey,
what's that bright stuff we're
spraying water on anyway?
Huh?
What do you mean, what?
[FIREMAN B]
Wait, what is that?
[SOUGON]
Humans understand all phenomena
through writing and words.
Should those ideas be diluted,
will human beings still
recognize their dangers?
The answer is no.
When the core concept
of flame has vanished
people will be unable
to comprehend
what is burning
before their very eyes
and will lose any means
of dealing with it.
And once all the kanji in
a space have been devoured,
and their meanings eliminated,
the M.J.B.K. will be released
into the Logos World,
birthing the next M.J.B.K.,
which will in turn,
consume another kanji.
When all kanji have
lost the root concepts
associated with that chain,
modern society will
cease to exist.
Corrosion rate has
just passed 90%!
No.
[SAKURAKO] Commander's order
four six eight five. Shirobaco.
[COMPUTER VOICE]
Command acknowledged.
[SHOKO]
Commander!
[SAKURAKO]
All staff evacuate!
According to DEAVA protocols,
we have to abandon this base.
How is running away
supposed to help us?
At this rate, the damages--
[SAKURAKO]
They won't keep piling up.
I'll put a stop to it myself.
I'll go into the Logos World
and I'll take the
stone monument with me.
[HAYATO]
Commander.
[SAKURAKO] Our ace in the hole
and Sougon's Book of Verbalism
somehow cancel
each other out.
If the monument were to
be brought into the Logos,
the space would close
and prevent the loss
of the kanji's concept.
W-Wait. Wh-What about the
others? They're still in there.
We have to do
something for them.
[SAKURAKO] If Akira and
Maia are inside Aquarion
protected by Verbalism,
it might be possible to eject
them back into our dimension.
But you d-don't sound sure.
I'm taking a Vector.
Since all I'm doing is launching
directly into the Logos World,
even my piloting
skills should suffice.
Shoko, I'm counting
on you for support.
Hold on!
If you charge in like this,
won't your Vector melt?
If that's the case,
I'll grab some sunscreen.
[TSUTOMU] I can't believe
what I'm hearin'!
You're not allowed to just
do whatever you feel!
Once the portal opens,
there will be a
powerful backdraft
strong enough to turn this
whole base into a hot zone.
Kento, I leave the
evacuation in your hands.
You have my word.
Pump the brakes and listen!
You want us to run
off without you?
How exactly are we supposed to
get by if we leave you behind?
There'll be more
M.J.B.K.s, no doubt!
If I don't keep you alive today,
there won't be a
later to worry about.
[KARAN crying]
[TSUTOMU]
The hell'd it do?
[SAKURAKO]
It can't be.
Was that its refusal?
It won't save us.
Why save foolish humans?
In the end, I'm
powerless. Pathetic.
Subete is in that new Vector.
So, is this Master
Sougon's will? It can't be.
Master Sougon.
Please, I did the best I
could to fulfill my mission.
That's the limit for now.
You've merged too deeply with
the M.J.B.K. Time to withdraw.
Withdraw? What're you
telling me, Hayashi?
I haven't yet
completed my mission.
Leave now, before the M.J.B.K.
devours that concept.
My mission.
Hold on.
What is a mission? That word.
What does it even mean?
[SOUGON] And so humans,
through their own malevolence,
drew the curtain on
their very existence.
A not at all dissatisfying end.
Kaibuki.
[SHOKO]
I'm not sure why, Commander,
but the damage has
stopped spreading.
The flames are subsiding
in all sectors!
However,
there are some who
would save these fools,
rather than leave them
to their just desserts.
But how. Why?
I hear them.
They're calling to me!
It's all coming back.
I remember you now.
You stole Maia from me, but
I'm going to bring her back!
[SUBETE yells]
Their voices.
Cry out to be saved!
What the--?
You did it.
[SHOKO] By enveloping
themselves in flame,
the Vectors are
somehow insulated
from the external heat.
But how does it work?
With you on our side,
I'm okay not having answers.
Kaibuki.
Akira.
Genesis. M-Merge.
[MAIA, AKIRA]
Dance!
Aquarion!
[AKIRA, MAIA]
Zai.
You want flame?
This is the fire
of absolute resolve.
[AKIRA, MAIA]
Heat Haze Dance!
[M.J.B.K. B]
En. En. En. En. En. En. En.
Is that the best
you've got, Red Vector?
[SUBETE]
Maia.
Wait! No! I'm stuck!
[AKIRA] As long as people
cry out to be saved,
I will deliver
each and every one.
[AKIRA]
For I am...
...the Savior!
That Red Vector guy
even saved me.
[SUBETE]
Akira Kaibuki.
[AKIRA]
Subete Kenzaki.
Kai... Kaibuki!
Subete.
[HAYASHI] So tell me,
how was your first flight?
[SUBETE]
It was awful.
I'll never forget this.
I'll make Kaibuki pay.
[SOUGON] The Pendulum
of Fate swings yet again.
How will your eyes view
this planet when you arrive...
...o, Nesta?
[BOTH screaming]
[AKIRA]
What's wrong?
[KARAN] There's a giant
cicada buzzing around!
[AKIRA] I don't discriminate
when it comes to saving.
For I am--
[KARAN]
Yeah, yeah! Just do something!
[KOKONE]
He c-caught it!
[BOTH]
Wow! Our savior!
[KARAN] That is so much
better! Next, Episode 8.
[KOKONE]
"Pierce It! The Insect Part!"
[BOTH]
Wait, an insect?