[SAKAMOTO]
I'm sorry, sir.
[IWAGAMI]
Hello, Shoko.
It's been some time.
What's the trouble?
Why the petrified look?
Why do you think?
Isn't this the look
most people would have
if their father sent a
squad of armed men after them?
[IWAGAMI] You were in
harm's way by choice,
if memory serves.
Did I not tell you repeatedly
to cut all ties with DEAVA?
You refused to listen.
I see, and not
listening to you
is ample grounds
for having me killed?
[IWAGAMI]
Don't twist my words.
You know very well
I had no intention
of letting things go that far.
Even so,
DEAVA cannot
be allowed to exist!
Shoko! Do it now!
[SHOKO]
Dad!
--[SOLDIER B23] Freeze!
--[KENTO] Hey!
[SAKAMOTO]
Lower your weapon! Hold fire!
[SHOKO] Daddy, I need you
to snap out of this!
Shoko?
Sweetie, what're you doing here?
Oh, thank god you're back!
[IWAGAMI]
I don't... What's going on?
Where have I been?
Well, will you look at that.
He really was being
controlled by someone!
[SAKURAKO]
Captain Sakamoto,
thank you for putting yourself
on the line like this.
Good thing Shoko knew you.
Before dad let him go last year,
he'd been a part of our security
staff since I was a little girl.
Sakurako. Shoko's ability.
Did you have any idea?
I had a hunch,
but 'til now, I wasn't sure.
The technical term
for what she's able to do is
"Zero Verbalism Ability."
She absorbs writing's power.
Zero?
All that aside,
we now have a proper
chance of striking back.
Fate willing.
[KOBAYAKAWA] They've
released an announcement.
You'll be glad to know
DEAVA's been cleared
of all terrorism charges.
Officially.
Welcome back.
Now show me what you can do.
[HAYATO]
Yes, sir.
[SUBETE]
It is time.
Come with me.
I will show you the truth of
that long ago moonlit night.
[HAYATO] I realize most of you
have never seen me before
nor have any clue who I am.
My name's Hayato Kujyo.
I'm a second year student
at Seisou's School of
Politics and Economics.
I'm also a member of
the organization, DEAVA.
I'll have to ask you
to bear with me.
What I'm about to say
will sound beyond absurd.
But you have my word it's true.
We've been keeping a secret--
One that concerns
all of you. Directly.
Our civilization is in crisis.
The written word
is under attack.
In fact, it's on
the brink of extinction.
Surely no one
would deny the barrage
of inexplicable things
we've all witnessed
over the past few months.
Every one of them
was the result
of a written word
being corrupted.
DEAVA was formed to push back
against the onslaught
of that corruption,
to make things right again.
Believe it or not,
we've been fighting in
the shadows all this time
to protect you.
[SAKURAKO]
What's he doing?
[HAYATO]
You didn't know
because you weren't
allowed to know.
And you weren't
allowed to know
because we flat out
didn't trust you.
We feared you'd panic,
that none of you
would have what it takes
to stand up in a time of crisis.
Right or wrong,
we felt it best
to tell only a select few
what was really going on.
We didn't think the
public could handle it.
Well, he certainly
doesn't mince words.
[HAYATO] In reality,
our secrecy was arrogant.
Time and again, we won the day,
and you were none the wiser.
Then we lost one of our own.
A friend. A comrade.
When a loved one dies,
we have a whole slew of cheap,
sentimental platitudes
to choose from to help us
negotiate our grief.
"Until we meet again," we say.
Or if we don't
believe in an afterlife,
"He'll live on in our hearts."
Sorry...
But it's a load of bull!
When someone you love dies,
that's it!
Look at us!
We're flesh and blood!
Even if there is a soul,
what good does it do us?
You can't touch it!
Can't talk to it
or laugh at its jokes.
All you're left with
are a handful of synapses!
And that's it.
That's all that's left
of the guy you knew.
The real person is gone.
He made you laugh.
Drove you crazy.
He was a character, always.
And now he's...
...gone like a dream
you just awoke from.
He's gone.
And without him,
the fight's not just harder,
it's all but impossible
for us to win.
What we've lost
is irreplaceable.
Yet we... Yet we still
have to carry on.
We need your help!
We need comrades who are
willing to fight alongside us!
I have no right to
ask you this, I realize.
Not after keeping the
truth from you for so long.
All the same, I beg of you.
Give DEAVA the honor and
privilege of your strength!
Help us carry on
the fight! Please!
[slow clapping]
[applause]
[CROWD cheering, applauding]
What a hottie!
Oh, I know.
What a speech!
Tsutomu Domon. Hayato Kujyo.
Many lives will be saved
because of your voices.
What about me?
[M.J.B.K. vocalizing]
[HATANO]
Come on! Put your backs into it!
[ITO]
That's the way!
[ALL grunting]
[KENTO]
Heave!
[ALL grunting]
[KOBAYAKAWA] Keep at it,
everyone! Have faith!
[OKAZAKI]
For Hayato!
[ALL grunting]
[SAKURAKO gasps]
[SAKURAKO]
Akira...?
[AKIRA] Can I be a savior,
as I am right now?
[SAKURAKO gasps]
Vector Four?!
Who's the hell's flying it?
Zero Verbalism, huh?
If that's my big power, fine.
I can do this.
Swimsuits!
[TSUTOMU] Let me sit right down
and tell you a trivial tale.
I'm gonna bring 'em back.
Every smile in the world.
[SHOKO]
Because right here and now,
Tsutomu is with me.
And his voice still
moves through me!
Verbalize!
My name is Shoko Iwagami!
I am the smiling girl--
The girl Tsutomu made laugh!
Kaibuki, heading out!
[CROWD cheering]
[SUBETE]
What was it you said?
That the boy who saved you
that moonlit night is gone?
What if I told you
that person
never existed
in the first place?
[MAIA gasps]
[SUBETE] It's vague,
but I have the same memory.
In my mind's eye,
I'm reaching out my hand.
However...
When I awakened the
Book of Verbalism's power,
all falsehood
within me vanished.
That's when I realized the
memory was a fabrication.
[MAIA]
What are you talking about?
[SUBETE]
Open.
When we were children,
father implanted false
memories in our brains.
This machine, which uses
Verbalism, is how he did it.
[MAIA]
Okay, but why?
Well, actually--
I was rather hoping you could
shed some light on that
for both our sakes.
[HAYATO]
Genesis Merge!
[SHOKO]
Dash!
[AKIRA]
Genesis Merge!
[KARAN]
Blossom!
Aquarion!
[AKIRA, KARAN]
[HAYATO, SHOKO]
Jin!
[AKIRA, KARAN]
Rin!
[SUBETE]
Verbalize.
[NESTA] Oh, Subete.
Really, you're too kind.
Kindness has
nothing to do with it.
I simply want some answers.
May I hazard a guess
at your true motivation?
You might insist otherwise,
but I think you're still
attached to the little puppet.
Of course,
to achieve your ambition,
you have little choice but
to treat her like a tool.
A soulless pawn...
Though the one person
you're trying
to convince most
of this is yourself.
[SUBETE]
Be silent.
[MAIA screaming]
[RESEARCHER B]
He's doing it.
Connection successful!
[KUWASHIMA]
The girl will be the next step
in the evolution
of communication.
[IIDA]
She is a goddess.
One who will preside
over an age of peace.
Indeed.
[MAIA] I was born empty.
No more than a vessel.
[IIDA] What do you think?
Do you like it?
[CHILD MAIA]
Yes. It's very fun.
She's only just been born
and her motor skills
are off the charts.
And her intellect already
exceeds that of a ten-year-old.
In fact, her abilities and rate
of growth resemble Subete's.
Which bears out, since he's
the one who summoned her.
It's all so fascinating!
[MAIA] Why did I
come into the world?
And why was I here,
in this place?
I didn't know,
so I contented myself
with living life
as it was handed to me.
[IIDA]
Ta-dah!
What is a Maia Tsukigane?
You.
That's your name, sweetheart.
We're not addressing you
as a number anymore.
You were born on a full moon,
so the name fits well.
And of course,
there's your silver hair.
So you're Tsukigane,
which I think is adorable.
I don't understand.
Maybe she doesn't like it.
Didn't I tell you the moon
thing was too on the nose?
You realize the name
is just a signifier?
[IIDA]
A rose by any other name?
[MAIA] I didn't
understand my situation,
but I did feel a
certain sense of worth
to the men who cared for me.
[CHILD SUBETE]
It's been a while.
Do you remember me?
I'm the reason you're here.
I brought you into this world!
[CHILD MAIA gasps]
[CHILD SUBETE]
What's wrong?
Don't touch me! Yucky!
That's odd.
Nesta's memories are starting
to subconsciously
affect her perception.
And she's disgusted
by her intended.
Isn't that the start
of every great romance?
[CHILD MAIA] You're really
going to buy those for me?
[KUWASHIMA]
Laundry day's rather awkward
when you only have
one pair of clothes.
And besides,
I'm not buying them.
Nesta's footing the bill.
How do I look?
I think you look great.
Yes. Good color.
Thanks!
Hey, easy now.
[IIDA laughs]
[CHILD MAIA laughs]
What's that?
[IIDA]
Huh?
Oh, just something for my boy.
He's about to turn five.
It's adorable!
[IIDA laughs]
Think so?
[MAIA] I thought my
future would be filled
with days like that one.
How terribly wrong I was.
[KUWASHIMA]
What's the meaning of this?
[IIDA]
Secretive as you are,
we've had to
infer your intentions.
So we conducted an independent
study of the ancient writing.
[KUWASHIMA] And if what's
described here is true,
Maia wasn't brought forth
to usher in an era of peace,
but to end civilization
as we know it!
[IIDA]
She's not a goddess at all!
She's the devil! A being
sent here to destroy us!
Tell me we're mistaken,
sir! I implore you!
[SOUGON]
You are correct.
Only by first destroying
modern civilization
can humanity truly be connected.
That has been my objective
from the outset.
Nesta has relinquished her
flesh. The balance has shifted.
As we speak, the Logos World
crumbles to nothing.
In a few years,
distortions will
manifest on this plane.
They will attack words.
They will distort their
meanings and erase them.
And only then can my project
finally begin in earnest.
[IIDA]
How horrible.
There's nothing that
can be done for it now.
The girl walks among us.
The culture of the
written word is doomed.
[KUWASHIMA] How could you
use her like that?
Destroy.
[KUWASHIMA choking]
[IIDA]
Maia!
Come with me!
[IIDA, CHILD MAIA panting]
[CHILD MAIA]
What're you talking about?
--[crashing noise]
--[CHILD MAIA gasps, screams]
[IIDA] If I kill you,
you'll revert to spirit form
and return to the Logos World!
It must be done!
It's the only way!
[CHILD MAIA]
Stop! Stop!
I'm sorry! I can't let you live!
You're here to destroy us!
Maia... I'm sorry...
Forgive me. I must--
--[thump]
--[CHILD MAIA screams]
[coughing]
[GUARD A] Obstacle eliminated.
Recovering target.
[CHILD MAIA screams]
[SHOKO]
It was deflected?!
[HAYATO] An electromagnetic
induction net?!
Let me m-merge,
and I'll f-fight with you!
[HAYATO]
Not with that arm!
[KARAN]
Un, deux, trois!
Oh, yeah?
[KARAN]
Got it!
[M.J.B.K. howling]
[KARAN screams]
Karan!
Oh, god!
[KARAN]
What the...?!
Come and get me, you bastard!
[M.J.B.K. vocalizes]
[AKIRA screaming]
[MAIA screaming]
Help me! Someone!
Help me! Please!
Help... Someone... Please.
[AKIRA screaming]
[MAIA screaming]
The written
characters connected.
[RESEARCHER 23A] So how much
longer we keeping these kids
around for?
[RESEARCHER 23B] We're looking
for people to take 'em in.
I'm guessin' that means
none of 'em have families?
[RESEARCHER 23A] Well, they
were only here as a backup
in case Subete proved a failure.
[RESEARCHER 23B] Why hold on
to the spares, right?
[TOP BUNK BOY 23A]
Hey.
You better lay back down
and go to sleep.
They'll get mad.
[GUARD 23B]
The girl escaped!
[GUARD 23C]
Son of a--!
[CHILD MAIA sobbing]
Hello, who's out here?
[CHILD MAIA sniffs]
Who are you?
Don't be scared.
I'm not gonna hurt you.
[CHILD MAIA]
Liar.
He said... He said if I'm...
...if I'm allowed to live,
the world will be destroyed.
That can't be right.
He said, "You've come here
to destroy us." I heard him.
I don't want that to happen.
It's not fair!
The world's not gonna
be destroyed if you live.
That's not how it works.
[CHILD MAIA]
You're lying!
No, I'm not!
The world wlll never end!
You're a liar and you don't
know what you're talking about!
Don't worry.
If it ever looks like
the world's about to end
because of you...
...I'll save it! Promise!
I'll be your Savior!
What do you mean "Savior"?
I'll be there to stop
the end of the world for you.
So don't worry!
It's okay for you to live!
[CHILD MAIA bawling]
Of course. The one who
really saved me that night.
The void I've felt
inside since I was a kid,
I had no purpose without her.
[CHILD AKIRA]
Hey! Let me out of this thing!
[CHILD SUBETE] Father, please!
What are you doing?
[SOUGON]
Verbalize.
It'll be all right.
Remember what I said:
Whatever happens,
I'll save the world.
That's a promise!
But... you...
For I am... The Savior!
[ALL screaming]
[SOUGON]
From this point forward,
Maia's activities
are to be confined
to the training area
and living quarters only.
I will see to her
education myself.
Apart from her
strictly regulated interactions
with Subete,
she's to be cut off from all
other human contact.
Any semblance of
a normal childhood
will only harm her in the end.
[RESEARCHER 23A]
You said "Maia."
Is that the child's name?
[SOUGON]
Yes. Maia.
That much I'll give her.
[SHIZUKA]
You must be Akira.
It's been so long since this
home was blessed with a child.
Welcome, little one.
We're thrilled to have you.
Please think of us as mother and
father, if that isn't too pushy.
[CHILD AKIRA]
I... I have to...
[SHIZUKA]
Have to what, dear?
[AKIRA]
I have to become The Savior.
I made a promise.
[SHIZUKA]
Did you, now?
[CHILD AKIRA]
I don't remember why.
I just know I have to.
I have to become
The Savior and save the world.
[KOUNOSUKE]
Easy, son.
A man doesn't talk about his
dreams with tears in his eyes.
Nor does he let
his voice quaver.
Don't talk about becoming The
Savior like it's down the road.
Say to yourself,
"I am The Savior."
[CHILD AKIRA]
I am The Savior.
[KOUNOSUKE]
There ya go.
That's a voice I can believe.
We'll call you
The Savior from now on.
[AKIRA]
I am...
I am The Savior!
[KARAN gasps]
Oh, no!
What the hell's happening?!
I've lost control
of my Vector!
Genesis Merge!
[AKIRA]
Save! Aquarion!
Deava!
I know who I am.
I'll never forget!
Uh... okay.
That was...
The controls are
the same for all of us!
Kaibuki?
[AKIRA]
Lightning Speed!
[CHILD AKIRA]
For I am... The Savior!
[AKIRA]
I am... Maia's Savior!
[M.J.B.K. howling]
I'm coming for you.
I have to find to Akira.
And tell him... the truth.
[MAIA]
A long time ago,
there were two sisters
named Hanako and Kaguya.
[KOKONE]
I r-really loved that script.
[KARAN] When you say "a long
time ago," how long you mean?
[KOKONE]
The Heian Period, I think.
[MAIA] A thousand years.
Isn't writing amazing?
[KARAN] How long ago is
a thousand years, though?
[KOKONE] One t-twelfth of
twelve th-thousand years ago!
[KARAN]
Okay, now I'm just confused.
Episode 24!
[MAIA] "To Battle! With My
Existence on the Line."