[SUBETE]
You wanna be the Savior?
I can be the Destroyer.
Bastard. He is going down!
Hey! What's the big idea?
You are my foe. My enemy!
[AKIRA groaning]
Akira! What's wrong?
Force retrieve Vector 2!
Uh, right!
[SUBETE] Did Akira's voice
destabilize the word?
His Verbalism
Ability is impressive.
Heh. He ought to be
careful what he wishes for.
Rejoice, for today,
I set you free!
[M.J.B.K.]
Teki.
[SUBETE] This world must
be so boring for you.
The world you desire,
however, now, that...
[WOMAN] Please! Save me.
Somebody. Save me.
[SUBETE]
"Save me," she says.
How perfect. Aren't those just
the words you love to hear?
Who are you?
You, the one borrowing her
voice to speak, who are you?
[KOKONE]
Akira! Th-Thank goodness!
What has gotten
into you? Seriously.
I'm sorry. There's an enemy.
[MAIA]
Huh?
D-Don't push yourself!
Hey, hold it! Your Vector,
it's still a wreck!
[AKIRA]
No problem.
Back off! He bumped
into me first!
[MAN B] C'mon, I barely
grazed your shoulder!
Let go of it. I clearly had
my hand there first, you hag!
Foot on the gas, moron!
Where the hell do you
expect me to go, you idiot?
Verbalize.
[TSUTOMU]
[SHOKO] The M.J.B.K.'s influence
is manifesting everywhere.
At this point, the conflicts
are fairly spread out,
but if the word corrosion
rate rises much more,
they could de-volve into
major widespread rioting.
This one amplifies
latent hostility.
If we don't do something about
it fast, we're in for trouble.
Don't let your guards down,
guys. Y'hear me? Be careful.
[M.J.B.K.]
Teki. Bastard. Enemy. Teki.
Genesis Merge.
Pierce it!
[BOTH]
Aquarion!
[HAYATO, TSUTOMU]
Gyu!
[TSUTOMU] All right,
ya four-eyed fetishist,
time to get'cher freak on!
[HAYATO]
Cease your inane prattling.
We need to cautiously
assess the situation first,
you unfunny hack.
[TSUTOMU]
Huh? Get over yourself, bro!
Bein' popular with the ladies
has gone to your damn head.
Also, school swimsuits suck!
[HAYATO]
How dare you!
What gives you the right
to mock school swimsuits?
Up yours!
What gives you the
right to call me a hack?
All o' my shit is original!
Back off!
If you're going to mock
a part of my identity,
you're my enemy too!
[TSUTOMU]
You're an idiot!
Lame ass locker room Lotharios
like you are my enemy!
[HAYATO] Everyone knows the
first to call someone an idiot
is the idiot, you idiot!
[KENTO]
Sakurako,
something in the current
M.J.B.K.'s data caught my eye!
[SHOKO]
You're both being idiots!
Knock it off and get your
heads back in the game!
[TSUTOMU]
Stay out of it, Tits McGee!
[SHOKO]
Ugh!
Well that was unnecessary!
[SAKURAKO] It has to be
the M.J.B.K. causing this.
[HAYATO] Hey, boss,
stop lying about your age!
[TSUTOMU] Don't just stand there
like a mute. Give us orders!
[SAKURAKO]
Well-- Uh--
Command the operation,
ya middle-aged maid!
Well, Commander,
they do have a point.
[SAKURAKO growls]
[SAKURAKO] So you're
callin' me old now, too?
No wait, I meant, they need
orders. I like how old you are.
[SAKURAKO growls]
I know you're trying to flirt.
But you need to stop.
[TSUTOMU] I'm not done with
you by a long shot, idiot!
[HAYATO] You'll know when
I'm finished with you!
[alarm blaring]
[SHOKO] Vector 6, you
do not have clearance!
Why did you launch?
Uminagi, we have rules here!
I'm standing right here!
[SHOKO, SAKURAKO]
Uh...
Then who is it?
[AKIRA]
Hayato Kujyo, prepare to Merge.
Akira? What are you
doing piloting Vector 6?
Here we go.
[HAYATO]
Don't you dare!
Who would ever want
to Merge with you?
Genesis Merge. Now fly!
[HAYATO]
Idiot, stop! It won't work!
This is Karan's and my--!
[AKIRA]
Aquarion!
[HAYATO]
Absurd. It feels so good!
Big Brother got beat!
[KARAN yelling]
[SAKURAKO]
I don't care!
[ROBO GRYPHON caws]
[AKIRA, HAYATO]
Gai!
Dammit! He really
went out there?
[REPRESENTATIVE]
Following a vote
from the board of directors,
the current president, Mr.
Georges, will be replaced.
Effective immediately, the newly
appointed CEO and President
is Mr. Subete Kenzaki.
No! Impossible!
[HAYASHI]
I have to hand it to you.
I didn't think you'd take
back the company so easily.
[SUBETE] Only due to
the groundwork you laid.
He'd be proud.
And should now find
peace in his rest.
[HAYASHI]
Well then,
I believe it's back to
the research lab for me.
[NESTA]
You spoil me so.
Taking back your mother
and father's company
all for my benefit?
I've told you not to
come out unbidden.
[NESTA]
Was leaving wise?
The battle in the Logos
World is not yet over.
[SUBETE] If he's going to
be crushed under the weight
of his own dreams,
why involve myself?
Now, more importantly--
[NESTA]
What, earlier? What's the harm?
Don't chide me for
appearing when I want.
it's not like anyone
else can see me.
[SUBETE] A ghost should
not appear anywhere.
[NESTA]
Well, that's rather harsh.
The power your father
passed onto you
is identical to what he called
the Book of Verbalism.
But the one who
taught you to use it.
Well, that was me.
[NESTA]
In the frozen time,
created by written
language itself,
you trained extensively
to learn control
over your power of Verbalism.
It may've been a mere
moment in this world's time,
but how many days,
how many months,
did you truly spend there?
Were you there so long that
your heart has frozen, too?
No matter. I far prefer
you as you are now.
Those eyes. So much like his.
Twelve thousand years since
someone last gazed upon me.
Do not misunderstand.
You are no more than a tool
to accomplish my goals.
[NESTA] And I'm
perfectly fine with that.
[ROBO GRYPHON caws]
Out of everybody, why did
I have to Merge with you?
You gettin' in my way?
--[HAYATO] Way?
--[AKIRA] Are you my enemy?
[KARAN] Knock it off!
What're you doing to Big Bro?
[SAKURAKO]
Kaibuki, calm down this instant!
I will not! Anyone who gets
in the way is my enemy.
[M.J.B.K.] Teki. Enemy.
Everyone is your enemy! Teki.
That M.J.B.K., it's
speaking directly to Akira.
[M.J.B.K.]
Teki!
[grunting]
[screaming]
[SHOKO] We've lost our
link to Vectors 4 and 5.
Hayato! Tsutomu! If you
read, please respond!
Transfer control of Kaibuki's
Vector 6 back to us!
Force return!
[SHOKO]
Uh. Right!
Big Brother.
[KOKONE] Ts-Tsutomu. Hayato.
Wh-What should we do?
[SHOKO] Commander, we're
already short on Vectors.
[SAKURAKO] Our only real option
is to make do with what we have.
Sakurako, should we
call the Saigon Base?
Put in an emergency request?
[ALL gasp]
I don't know if it would
even arrive in time,
but if we can get it to Akira,
he might be able to pilot it.
[MAIA]
What's this about?
[KENTO] At the DEAVA branch
in Vietnam is the final Vector.
[SAKURAKO]
Kento.
[MAIA]
Is that true?
[SAKURAKO] It is, but...
it's not an option.
[KOKONE]
Wh-Why not?
Because 12 thousand
years ago that Vector...
...is the one that
destroyed the legend.
[SAKURAKO]
Now,
I'm sure not even all this
is enough to contain you.
But this time, they will
shoot. Don't test me. Okay?
A-Akira.
[SAKURAKO]
I'm sorry,
but you simply cannot currently
be trusted to be left alone.
[KENTO]
The Vectors we've used until now
were assembled using modern
technology and resources
based on blueprints
dug up in ancient ruins.
However, this "final
Vector" I mentioned,
that's a whole different beast.
You see, deep within the ruins
of the writing culture,
it was enshrined at some
kind of central altar.
It was as though the Vector
had been sealed away,
as though even approaching
it was taboo.
And emblazoned on the
walls were these words,
"Destroyer of Legends."
[SHOKO]
And now it's at our Saigon Base?
What we managed to
salvage of it is,
but we could hardly
have called it a success.
No matter how we tuned it, the
machine never once activated.
To make matters worse,
there were rumors that some
mysterious magical energy
was hidden inside it.
During one activation attempt,
every engineer and
test pilot involved,
every single person working
on the restoration project,
just vanished without a trace.
And then, the poor
maintenance crew,
just trying to clean
the damn thing,
all ended up developing
severe cognitive impairments.
[SHOKO]
That's some bad juju!
How can we expect Akira to
pilot a machine like that?
[KENTO]
I don't know.
I've been asking myself
the same thing.
But how else are we supposed
to save Hayato and Tsutomu?
[SHOKO]
Still, though.
[KENTO]
It may not matter.
We'll only have a chance
to find out if it arrives
from the Saigon Base in time.
I see, so you're all against me.
[AKIRA]
So be it!
[SAKURAKO gasps]
[KARAN screams]
Oh boy, nothing gets me pumped
up like a good fistfight!
Akira! Y-You have to stop!
She's right! This is not
who you should be fighting!
[GUARD]
Huh? What's he doin'?
It's coming.
It will soon be here.
Something's coming? What is it?
That which always
comes to a Savior.
One thing.
It can only be destiny!
[SAKURAKO]
The Logos Monument? Why?
[NESTA] Looks like it's
regained consciousness
in response to your awakening.
[SUBETE]
I see. And I feel it.
[NESTA]
Yes.
The accursed power which
once burned him and me.
[LOGOS MONUMENT howling]
[KARAN]
What's it doing?
[KOKONE] It's f-freakin'
me out, that's what.
[LOGOS MONUMENT] I must
consume. Kiryu. The traitor.
Kiryu?
[LOGOS MONUMENT]
You who are strong of will,
tell me, what is it you seek?
Tell you what it is I seek?
[LOGOS MONUMENT]
It seems that which you seek
and that which we must
destroy are identical.
[LOGOS MONUMENT]
Thus, have we awakened.
Thus, have we resonated.
And thus, shall we
bestow upon you
the power which consumes all.
No, wait!
It's not safe!
[MAIA]
Akira!
What the actual
hell is all this?
[GUARDS murmuring]
Akira Kaibuki is the enemy?
[KARAN]
Enemy.
[OPERATOR A] Vector 3
quantum engine has failed!
[KOKONE]
Verbalize.
[OPERATOR A] Vector 6
showing the same pulse!
Launch gate is
opening on its own.
I can't regain
control on our end!
[KARAN]
Verbalize.
[OPERATOR B] Kokone
Kikogami and Karan Uminagi
show Verbalism readings of zero.
Vital signs in the red.
[SHOKO]
Commander.
Vectors 3 and 6 have
both just launched!
[MAIA]
I'm going, too!
No, wait! Tsukigane!
I'm going to bring them back!
[SAKURAKO] You are? And how
are you gonna do that?
[MAIA]
I don't know,
but I can't let Akira
do everything himself!
Akira, enemy.
Akira is the enemy.
My enemy. You are my enemy.
[M.J.B.K.]
Teki. Enemy.
[KENTO] It's like that M.J.B.K.
is acting in response to Akira.
[SHOKO gasps]
I need power to strike
down my enemies. To me!
[MAIA]
Akira!
Where'd that come from?
[SHOKO]
What Vector is that?
[KENTO]
That machine... It can't be.
[SHOKO gasps]
[SHOKO] You don't mean that's
the Destroyer of Legends
you were telling us about?
I don't believe it.
It just teleported
here from Vietnam.
And nobody's piloting it.
[SAKURAKO] The Logos Monument
must've been its activation key.
What're you saying?
It's the final
vector: Vector-Ga.
[AKIRA]
Verbalize.
I'm being pulled in!
[M.J.B.K.]
Teki. Enemy.
Why isn't it working?
We Merged, but my
cockpit hasn't changed.
[SAN]
I will consume all.
I will consume all. Devour all.
[KENTO whimpers]
[SHOKO]
I don't get what's happening.
It's swallowing 'em. The
M.J.B.K. and its words.
Oh man, this is
just like when...
I understand now.
Why the Monument
worked as a counter
to the Book of Verbalism.
[SAKURAKO] It's because it's
an entity that devours words,
concept and all.
It needs them.
[KENTO]
So then--
[SAKURAKO] The M.J.B.K.s and
the Monument are similar beings.
[SUBETE] Having touched
his voice, I understand.
Savior. That word has lost all
meaning or reason for Akira.
And without a true
sense of purpose,
he's driven only by instinct
telling him he must become
what he can no
longer believe in.
Because saving things is the
only way he knows he exists.
One day, he will realize
there's no one left to save.
He destroyed them all because he
decided they were his enemies.
[SUBETE] And so, he will
continue seeking new enemies.
All that lies at the end
of his path is ruin.
Word corrosion rate
is rising rapidly!
It's already exceeded 80%!
[SAKURAKO]
That Aquarion is consuming
the M.J.B.K.'s
word and concepts.
There might as well be
two M.J.B.K.s fighting
each other out there!
So does that mean Akira's
turned into an M.J.B.K.?
[AKIRA panting]
Enemy. I will strike you down!
Akira, stop this! Our friends
are still trapped inside!
Enemies! Not friends!
Not even people! Enemies!
Akira!
[gasps]
I am the Savior.
And I will save the world.
Enemies. That's us. Enemies!
[gasps]
Damn it, Akira, stop!
What is she doing?
Maia, get out of there!
[MAIA]
Save me!
[M.J.B.K.]
Techi!
[MAIA gasps]
I admit it. I did all
I could to seek out enemies.
But that.... that
is not who I am.
[M.J.B.K.]
Enemy. Teki!
[AKIRA]
What I am is a Savior!
Now, Maia! Come!
Okay!
[AKIRA] Even if there's
nothing at the end of it all,
I'll keep right on
doing what I do.
As long and as far as I can.
[MAIA]
Yes, as far as we can!
[BOTH]
Into infinity.
Fist of Unending Salvation!
[M.J.B.K.]
Teki. Enemy. Enemy! Teki!
[HAYATO]
What were we just doing?
[KOKONE, KARAN gasp]
[SUBETE]
Heh. Oh, I love it.
Now, Nesta. Preparations.
Preparations?
[SUBETE] To destroy
the world he would save,
I must awaken Aquarion Logos.
[KOKONE] Our next reading
theater performance!
[TSUTOMU]
I'm playin' an old lady again?
[HAYATO] You want me to
learn all of these lines
in time for the school festival?
Between that, seminar,
debate club,
and work for the senator,
when will I sleep?
Is the manager a total sadist?
[TSUTOMU]
But you read 'em so smooth!
[KOKONE]
Wish I could do that!
[HAYATO]
Give it a rest.
[KOKONE]
Episode 18.
[HAYATO]
"Howl! An Honest Beaten Dog."
[KOKONE]
H-Hayato.
[TSUTOMU]
Mucho tsundere!