[SAKURAKO] It's been almost
a month since our battle
with Sougon Kenzaki's enormous
"Nothingness" M.J.B.K.
Sougon, the co-founder,
lead developer, and now CEO
of the world's largest social
networking service, Nesta,
has suddenly vanished,
along with his son,
Subete Kenzaki.
Given their obviously
high public profile,
this has seen major news
coverage every day since.
As speculation over their
whereabouts ran rampant,
Nesta's stock price
began to plummet.
There was concern over the
company's continued existence.
Until the appointment of a new
president and upper management
eased public concerns over
their ability to recover.
Although numerous
talks have been held
in regards to what
will become of DEAVA,
consensus has
yet to be reached.
Further deliberations
will likely touch on
whether the organization
will be permitted to continue.
[SAKURAKO sighs]
[beeping]
[SAKURAKO]
Who's there?
You can't be.
[SAKURAKO]
You are!
[SOUGON]
In times past,
humanity was at one
with the world of truth,
but the written word, for
all we prospered from it,
wrought incalculable suffering.
[TSUTOMU]
A humanoid M.J.B.K.?
Jeez, I guess nothin's
sacred with these things.
So why is he just
staring at the manager?
[SAKURAKO]
Meow?
There are many animals,
such as ducklings,
which imprint on the first
living being they see.
Perhaps this is a
similar situation?
[SHOKO]
So, what?
You're saying he thinks of
the manager as his mother?
Manager Mama!
[SAKURAKO]
Hey, meow! That's rude!
I can't have a kid this big,
people will think I'm old!
S-So, what do we call him?
[TSUTOMU] Yeah, I'd feel bad
if he didn't have a name.
We can't just call him M.J.B.K.
He has a point. Any ideas?
[AKIRA]
Hito.
[TSUTOMU groans]
[TSUTOMU] "Hito" because it
means person? Too on the nose!
Isn't that like naming
your dog, Dog?
Or even worse, naming your
refrigerator, Rey Frigerator?
[KARAN]
No one names their refrigerator.
[KOKONE] B-But... I think
Hito is a g-good name.
[MAIA]
Easy to remember, too.
Fine, whatever. We can
call him Hito for now.
[SAKURAKO]
Nice to meet you, Hito.
[KENTO] Why do you think
the little guy showed up?
Without Sougon around,
there should be no way
for distorted words
to become M.J.B.K.s.
[SAKURAKO] I've been
giving that some thought.
Best I can figure is
maybe the Logos World
was somehow destabilized
during our last battle.
Meaning who knows
what could happen next.
We've gotta get the
Vectors fixed up fast.
Ugh. Too bad they
slashed our budget.
[SHOKO] Then I'll go tell them
to raise it for you. No bigs.
[BOTH]
Sorry? Tell who?
What's up?
You tell me. Why're we here?
[AKIRA]
Because of this weight,
Shinjuku's out of
the way, but I got it,
so coming here was worth it.
[MAIA]
I see. You sound happy.
[WORKMAN]
Yo, more to the left.
[MAIA] Anyway, Sougon
and Subete died, right?
I can't imagine how they
could've survived that.
If they had, then
there's no reason
they'd still be missing
after a whole month.
But still...
Which outcome would
you prefer to be true?
I don't know anymore.
Maybe that's the
reason I came here.
[MAIA] Am I just being silly?
I mean, it's all over now.
[AKIRA]
Not yet. Hito still came.
So M.J.B.K.s that threaten us
are sure to keep coming as well.
My battle has not yet been won.
[SAKURAKO] This is my apartment.
Where I live. Understand?
I can't leave you with
someone I don't know.
C'mon upstairs, Hito.
Oh, Ms. Soda, how are you?
[SAKURAKO]
Evening. Good. Heading out?
[OHTSUKA] Yeah, down to the
diner to finish my report.
Fewer distractions than at home.
I hear ya there.
College is tough.
[OHTSUKA] Hey, d'ja see
the bulletin board?
The day caredown on one
says they're increasing
the number of kids
they can take overnight.
[SAKURAKO]
Oh, they are, huh?
[SAKURAKO giggles]
[OHTSUKA]
Well, see ya later.
[SAKURAKO]
Ohtsuka, wait!
Great, someone else
who thinks I'm old now.
Are you hungry? Or--
No, I guess you don't eat.
That? You noticed, huh?
That's my treasure.
Based on the debriefing reports
of both Akira Kaibuki
and Maia Tsukigane,
the likelihood of Sougon
Kenzaki having survived
is considered extremely low.
This means that the M.J.B.K.
threat has effectively passed,
and that the DEAVA
organization was instrumental
in saving the world.
Sougon Kenzaki.
You can read, right?
Okay!
Here. "Dog." Do you understand?
Woof! Woof!
[HITO]
[SAKURAKO giggles]
Yes! Nicely done! What's next?
Well?
Yes, it says crab!
And, how 'bout.
[HITO]
Bang.
[groaning]
[SAKURAKO]
Oh! No! You got me!
You're amazing, Hito!
Best student ever!
Let's see, next.
What's this one?
[MAIA]
"Preposterous!
You claim to be that
Urashima Mantarou?"
"Indeed! I have waited
for this moment.
At last, I shall
have my revenge!"
[MAIA]
"Curse you!
To arms! My turtle warriors!
To arms! To arms!"
[KOKONE]
"I am sorry, Princess Otohime.
Your t-turtle army is no more.
You sacrificed all of them
yesterday to m-make your soup."
[MAIA]
"And they were delicious!
But oh, what a blunder!"
"Evil was vanquished, and we
all lived happily ever after."
[HAYATO clears throat]
"Ever after!"
Hito!
H-Hito, you d-did
a really g-good job!
[TSUTOMU] So like, if the
battle's over and all,
do we get to keep
the Club going?
Or is this the last hurrah?
Not sure yet.
"The matter is still
up for discussion."
[MAIA] If we do get to keep
going, Hito should join, too.
[KARAN]
Totally!
So he can read but
he's unable to speak.
Is that common among M.J.B.K.s?
[TSUTOMU] Does it really
matter? Don't stress, man.
[KARAN giggles]
[SAKURAKO chuckles]
[TSUTOMU]
He's good. With that penmanship?
Y-You got it right!
My penmanship's fine!
[TSUTOMU yelping]
[TSUTOMU]
Ah! Hey! Ah! Ow!
[SHOKO] You do so well
with reading, Hito.
Hopefully you can learn
to speak eventually, too.
Wouldn't that be something.
Hey, is Hayato around?
[SUZUKI]
Yeah, or Kokone?
No, they've gone
home for the day.
What?
[HITO]
Hito!
[SUZUKI yelping]
[MAIA]
No!
As I suspected, you're the
written word, aren't you?
He is the written
word personified.
So, he tries to communicate
the words he sees literally.
But people don't always
mean things literally.
Like, when you see
a commenter online
saying they'll kill you
or they want you to die.
They don't actually mean it.
[AKIRA] That's not something
you can tell from words alone.
[SAKURAKO]
Yes, you're right.
Even if it's intended
lightly, as a joke,
it doesn't weaken the meaning
of the words you wrote.
[AKIRA]
It's tricky.
Your words may come across
with a different meaning
than you intend.
When you think of it that
way, writing is kinda scary.
The meanings words carry can say
so much more than
the writer felt.
So if all you're focused on
is the words being used,
your heart can be left out.
Superficial bonds
built on writing.
That's what Sougon Kenzaki
was worried about.
Like that Sougon
person was saying,
it may be dangerous
to connect so easily
with others through writing.
That can't be true.
There must be people
who were saved
by the bonds they
made with writing.
Hey, if Hito is writing in human
form, where does his heart lie?
Is he good or evil?
Does he even have
a voice of his own?
Good and evil don't
apply. It has no will.
[OHTSUKA]
There ya go.
Now, don't tell
your mommy, 'kay?
[CHILD]
'Kay!
[footsteps]
[MOTHER]
Tatsuya! Sorry I'm late, hon.
[SAKURAKO]
I demand an explanation, sir!
What is this about the
Logos World, and ampules,
and the so-called
M.J.B.K.s born from them?
Is everything written
in here the truth?
[SAKURAKO] What are you trying
to do, destroy the world?
[SOUGON]
The opposite.
[SAKURAKO]
What?
[SOUGON]
Humans have depended too much
on written communication.
So that we may all have
meaningful connections,
connections of the heart,
the culture of writing
must be destroyed.
Are you saying you
think connections
formed through writing
are not valid?
Yes, I am.
[SAKURAKO growls, grunts]
Report to Human Resources.
They'll have your severance.
Thank you, but no.
I'll be taking something
else as my compensation.
I won't let you have
your way with this world.
We did it. We saved
the world from him.
I won, and he lost his life.
And yet...
[ANCHOR] On the BBS the culprit
is believed to have posted on,
one post said he had
given a bomb to a child
commuting to day care.
Due to his heinous methods,
police have requested disclosure
of the poster's IP address.
However. because the postings...
[SAKURAKO]
What is it?
Authorities are hard pressed...
[SAKURAKO] You understand those
words? Do you know something?
[HITO grunting]
[SAKURAKO]
Huh?
Next door?
[door bell rings]
Ah, Ms. Soda, how are ya?
[OHTSUKA yelps]
Where'd you put the bomb?
What're you talking about?
[SAKURAKO]
Don't screw with me.
[OHTSUKA]
Heh.
I dunno.
I just gave it to one of those
kids at the daycare downstairs.
Why would you do that?
[KID crying]
Just listen. They're
always so loud and-- Uh!
[SAKURAKO]
I have to hurry!
We're calling everyone who
left their children here today
and telling them to
check the contents
of their children's bags.
But given the time,
there are some people
we've been unable to
get in contact with.
I've talked to the
police, as well.
They say they'll go to
the houses of the people
we couldn't reach.
But they don't know if they can
make it by the announced time.
Do you have a list of who
left their kids here today?
I'll start with
the closest house
and work my way from there.
[SAKURAKO]
Excellent.
[HAYATO]
I got in touch with the others,
but I'm afraid it still
won't give us enough time.
[SAKURAKO] It'll have to.
There's no other way.
Anyway, let everybody know.
Make sure to be available
by both cell and Aquariphone.
[SAKURAKO]
Hito, go back to the house!
[phone ringing]
[MAN A]
Uh?
--[WOMAN A chuckling]
--[phone ringing]
[phones ringing]
[MAN B]
If it's this guy,
I spotted him speaking
to a boy in Asagaya Park.
[WOMAN B] I saw that, too. In
front of the restrooms, I think.
[WOMAN C] Someone who
might've been his mom
had the boy wait while
she went to the bathroom.
I noticed her because
she was wearing
the same yellow coat as me.
[MAN C]
I saw a mother and child
head into the shopping
street from Asagaya.
The mother was wearing
a showy yellow coat.
Wait, yes.
[WOMAN D] I think this
was that mother and child.
They were shopping
at the fishmonger
in the shopping street.
It's a place called Uohachiya.
[MAN D]
Uohachiya is my store.
I believe the person you're
all talking about is Ms. Takai.
As I recall, she did come
shop at my place again today.
Takai.
Found him. Tatsuya Takai.
And their address
is... It's close!
Yeah. Just wait for me, and
I'll be there in a minute.
Okay, if you're sure.
The manager says
she's going by herself.
[SHOKO gasps]
Isn't that kinda out
of character for her?
Not after what happened to her
in the same situation
in the past.
[SAKURAKO] President Sougon,
bonds formed through writing
are not wrong in any way.
Even if they're shallow
or fleeting relationships,
they can still save lives.
Like they did for me
once upon a time.
[EMERGENCY RESPONDER]
Do you see anyone near you?
This is the warehouse.
It's far from the store.
I called for help, but
they'll take too long.
[EMERGENCY RESPONDER] I'm sorry,
the ambulances are all out now.
It'll be 30 minutes
at the earliest.
I can't... can't breathe.
[EMERGENCY RESPONDER] Just
hang in there and be strong!
We'll be there as soon
as we can, I promise!
Help... me.
[MAN E]
Seriously?
[WOMAN E]
Someone nearby, go help her!
[MAN F]
She's messing with us.
[MAN G]
It'll take me two hours.
[WOMAN F] Wasn't there a
little earthquake just now?
[WOMAN G]
If this is true, it's awful.
Stop the car.
[SAKURAKO groaning]
[SAKURAKO crying]
What?
Where's his bookbag?
[CHILD crying]
Run! Hurry!
[SAKURAKO coughing]
I had to defeat Sougon
so I could save the world.
But not for peace. Not to
protect the culture of writing.
Those were just
lies I told myself.
This was personal,
I was mad at him.
The bonds of writing are
what had brought us together.
He saved me, but
denied those bonds.
That light, that hope,
it shone on me.
Then he made it feel as though
it never happened. So...
So I fought, and I fought
because I wanted to somehow try
and convince President Sougon,
"You're wrong,
don't you get it?"
I was selfish.
[laughs]
Honestly... I'm the worst.
[HITO]
Hito!
L-Look!
What is that?
It takes a true voice to lend
strength to the written word.
[wood clattering]
Hito, what...?
[SAKURAKO]
Hito, you can't do this.
Just leave me. At
least get yourself out.
[HAYATO]
Commander!
Don't tell me she's--
[HAYATO, SOKO gasp]
[KENTO]
Manager!
[TSUTOMU]
We got'cha. Hang in there!
[KARAN]
Hito! No! No!
[TSUTOMU] You can't get taken
out by somethin' like this!
You're an M.J.B.K., aren'tcha?
He's not. At least not anymore.
Hito, no!
[HITO]
Thank you.
Thank you for playing
with me, Manager Mama.
[AKIRA] That was your
own true voice just now.
And now that you have your
own will, you're human.
He is... He's human.
Dummy. Who're you callin'
"Mama"? I'm not that old.
You'll make me mad... Hito...
[SAKURAKO]
Wait, you're telling me
none of you know
what nata de coco is?
[KARAN]
Nata? Coco?
[KOKONE]
S-Sorry, Manager, I don't.
[SHOKO] I'm guessing it has
something to do with coconut?
[SAKURAKO] This generation
gap should not be so wide!
I'm only around 30,
for cryin' out loud!
[SHOKO] Like bubbles, fads
never last. Next: Episode 15!
[KARAN]
"Ah! Days of Our Youth!"
[SAKURAKO]
Ya better watch, or else!