[TSUTOMU]
No, seriously!
It's called "Destiny
on the Asagaya."
[SCHOOLGIRL]
Yeah, no thanks.
[groans]
More like "Dissed
on the Asagaya."
Heavens! A real live
pick-up artist!
What do we do? I'm scared!
[SHOKO] Calm down.
We'll just ignore him.
[TSUTOMU] 'Ey, Shoko!
Wanna find your destiny with me?
I'll buy you a ton a chocolates!
Sorry?
[AKIRA]
What's up?
[MAIA]
Uh...
Nothin'.
[AKIRA]
Hm?
Hi-ee! It's Destiny
on the Asagaya.
Bascially a romance-themed
scavenger hunt around town
where all the contestants
participate as couples.
The couple that completes
the most objectives,
in a super-duper,
lovey way, of course,
wins a coupon good for all sorts
of fun couples activities!
Who does Karan love, you ask?
Why, her fans, silly!
[KOKONE giggles]
Is this some new type
of Reading Theatre?
No, I'm practicing
'cause I'm the emcee.
Hey!
[AKIRA] Maia, you an'
me are taking part.
[MAIA]
Huh?
[AKIRA] That's required
headgear for a Savior.
[MAIA]
You need a crown?
Y'know they're just
plastic, right?
You said the contestants
have to be a couple?
[KARAN] Yeah, but not
necessarily a real one.
[MAIA]
What're you getting at?
Heh, heh. You two should
pretend to be lovers.
Pretend to be... what?
[KARAN]
What?! Why would you do that?!
You don't actually
have to be a thing.
It's just for the contest!
Oh god. Tsutomu?!
What can I say?
It just happened.
Man, rippin' me off!
Shoulda secured the copyright
when I had the chance!
News flash: No one cares.
Anyways, it sounds fun.
And I'm off work that day.
[TSUTOMU] Let's practice.
"Shoko, my love!"
But why pretend?
Wanna go out for real?
Yeah, okay.
--[SAKURAKO] Ah?
--[TSUTOMU] Really?
[SHOKO] How much can
I really know about you
till we've gone out, right?
There's a distinct possibility
I'll fall head over heels.
But just to be clear,
let's set some boundaries.
Until we've gotten
to that point...
...no "boyfriend
girlfriend" stuff.
Uh, yeah, 'course!
You're so mature
for your age, Shoko.
Oh wow.
So... romantic.
What's boyfriend
girlfriend stuff?
[KARAN]
Uh?
[KOKONE]
Uhh.
Uh...
L-Like...
Kissing!
Kissing?
[KARAN]
Hugging, too.
[MAIA]
Right. What else?
[KARAN]
Uh. Well, it's kinda pervy.
I'm so confused.
Explain in detail.
Oh, jeez, Maia! It's so gross!
You know what I'm talking about.
--[MAIA] Karan!
--Don't make me say it!
Oh, my darling, I...
We can't fight this, George.
What am I watching?
[KARAN] You're killin' me.
This is how people kiss.
It's what you do with the
person you love. For starters.
[ACTOR A]
Oh, my darling...
With the person you love?
Well, to be fair,
in some countries,
it's just how people say hello,
but these two are
definitely in love.
Fascinating.
[gasps]
Wait. So, I have to do this
sort of thing with Akira?
[gasps]
Oh, ew, no. You'll just
need to fake it. Easy.
[MAIA] But won't our opponents
smell the ruse from a mile away?
You'll just have to fake it
convincingly then, won't you?
Oh. I see. I'll make
sure no one catches on.
[Where're you going?
J-Just m-making some tea.
[MAIA]
What's taking so long?
[KOKONE gasps] Oh. S-Sorry, I--
[MAIA]
You should go in my place.
[KOKONE]
Huh?
[MAIA] You're better
suited to it, really.
Because of all the movies
you've watched, I mean.
You know how proper couples
are supposed to behave.
[KOKONE]
R-Romantic movies are just
a g-g-guilty pleasure for me.
And b-besides, Akira asked
y-you to go with him.
I'd just mess things up.
[MAIA]
The guy's a consummate imbecile.
[KOKONE] B-But... he
chose you. Isn't that...?
[MAIA]
Huh?
[KOKONE] D-doesn't that
make you feel good?
[MAIA]
How so?
W-Well, some p-part of you
must think that A-Akira is...
[MAIA groans]
[MAIA]
He's a pain.
[KOKONE]
Huh?
[MAIA] You have to
watch him like a hawk.
Take your eyes off
the idiot for a second,
there's no telling
the havoc he'll cause.
'Cept the one part of me that
doesn't think he's a pain
worries about him constantly.
That s-sounds--
[MAIA]
Huh?
[KOKONE]
Uhh...
[KOKONE] M-Maybe Akira
f-feels the same way.
[MAIA]
Hm?
[KOKONE] I mean, h-he's
always l-looking at you.
Always s-seems to be worried.
[MAIA]
That doesn't make me special.
[KOKONE]
Huh?
[MAIA]
He's that way with everyone.
He's the Savior.
Sorry! Hope you
weren't waiting long!
[smack]
Ouch.
The event coordinators
could be monitoring us
from several angles.
We give them any reason to
suspect we're not a real couple,
the jig is up.
[AKIRA]
Mh-hm.
Sorry! Hope you
weren't waiting long!
No. Only just got here.
[MAIA]
Passable. It'll have to do.
Since when are you
two scene partners?
[SHOKO]
G'morning. Nice to see you.
Check it out! She's
wearing this on our date!
[SHOKO] I don't see what
you're excited about
it's just a school uniform.
Which is the perfect choice!
A uniform is the best outfit
a girl has in her wardrobe!
Curses, perhaps we
should have opted
to go with our flightsuits.
Why, are we launching?
[HAYATO]
Bit early to be this pumped.
Milkman, hey! Look at you!
Couldn't resist the chance to
watch our lovey-dovey antics,
hmm?
Personal space.
Actually we're participating.
[TSUTOMU]
Hm? We?
Oh. G-good... Good m-morning.
[TSUTOMU] Dude, you got
some nerve bringin' Kokone.
Little outta your
league, don'cha think?
It isn't like that! If you
must know, she asked me.
[AKIRA] The Sovereign
Crown is still goin' to me.
Yeah, you know you're the only
one trying for third, right?
[gasps]
[CROWD cheering]
Keep an eye out
for the checkpoints.
And the Trials of Love, 'kay?
And remember!
For true love, no trial
is ever insurmountable!
[CROWD cheering]
Great.
[TSUTOMU]
Uh?
Come on, sweetie. Cheer!
[SHOKO giggles]
[KARAN]
How well you do is measured
by how much your
heart's in the game,
so aim high and good luck!
When the points are tallied,
the couple with the highest
score will be our winners!
And now, without further ado,
let Destiny in Asagaya begin!
[whistle blows]
So, Shoko.
Eh?
Well, all right,
but I have to admit it's
still sort of off-putting.
[TSUTOMU]
Oh.
Takin' it slow! Classic
romance for the win!
[AKIRA]
Seriously?
C'mon, bro!
Don't you want the grand prize?
[AKIRA]
I'm going for third place.
[MAIA] The genuine couples
are quite impressive.
They seem so in love.
[HAYATO]
Hmm. What's our mode of attack?
[KARAN]
Hey, Big Brother.
Promise me you
have Kokone's back.
I promise.
Let's do this.
[MAIA]
Huh?
Akira, evidently couples
like to hold hands.
Easy now, let's not
get carried away.
They're not watching
us around every corner.
I see. Well, all right then.
You okay?
Don't start.
I'm simply wondering what manner
of trials are in store for us.
[AKIRA]
No idea.
But if it comes to
it, I'll save you.
I'll always save you,
for I am the Savior.
I know, you always say that.
Do me a favor,
don't save me today.
Okay.
[BOYFRIEND A]
I love you!
[RESIDENT A]
What's wrong with him?
[RESIDENT B]
Youth.
I love you!
[BOYFRIEND C]
Tha-That's pretty
good Verbalism skill.
Volume mostly.
Mind if I ask what
you hope to accomplish?
[KOKONE]
Huh?
'Cause, depending
on your objective,
we might want to focus
our efforts elsewhere
in the interest of efficiency.
[AKIRA]
What're you pissed about?
[MAIA]
I'm not.
[AKIRA]
Sure.
[MAIA]
I said I'm not.
You need.
[MAIA]
Stop it!
[STAFF MEMBER B chuckles]
[STAFF MEMBER B]
Trouble in paradise?
You'll need to kiss n' make
up before this next hurdle.
[MAIA gasps]
[MAIA]
Oh no. The Trial of Love!
The objective here's
simple enough.
You have to take a
cutesy couple's photo.
And how does that work, exactly?
Like this.
[MAIA] Idiot. I'm not
even in the frame.
It's good!
I didn't say anything!
No problem, I can
take it for you.
Let's see ya give your
man a nice big hug.
In public?
We got the lowest
score they give out.
My neck still hurts. Uh?
Look out!
What the--? Uh.
I thought I told you
not to save me!
[SHOKO gasps]
[TSUTOMU] Hey, hey! How's
my second favorite couple?
Hold on. Who's "Mew Mew"?
[BOYFRIEND D]
Just a friend! I swear!
[GIRLFRIEND A] A friend?
Who texts, "can't wait..."
Oh dear.
Love trial.
You're supposed to give
your significant other
access to your phone.
[AKIRA]
Sanae Ando? Yoshiko Inoue? Okay.
What? They're with DEAVA.
How long you been friends
with the cleaning staff?
[STAFF MEMBER C] I need to
see your recent texts, please.
[MAIA]
"Sorry. I'm going to be late."
[AKIRA] "No big. The Savior
isn't bothered at all."
Is that like some sorta code?
Y'know, I like your commitment.
That's some high-level role
play. Twenty points! Boom!
Ha, ha!
Yeah!
Not bad. Color me impressed.
'Course, Shoko an'
I got 30 points,
but what're you gonna do?
'Scuse me?
She was the only person
in my contacts.
And the only thing in
my inbox was from her.
[SHOKO]
Yeah, that may sound sweet,
but his outbox paints
a very different picture.
All those girls were before you!
[MAIA gasping]
Sorry, Sanae. Yoshiko.
You're deleting them?
Trial of Love number four.
Stay strong. Stay together.
Show us how much
you adore each other!
It's the Princess-Carrying
Endurance Test!
How long can you last?
Sorry. I must weigh a ton.
No way!
If I think of the weight
in boobs and buns,
I'm happy to bear the burden!
So I am like a bag of rocks.
[MAIA grunting]
[KARAN]
Go for it, couples!
The less you end up with,
the higher you score!
What're you doing?
I'm not stupid.
We almost kissed.
And that woulda
been a problem, why?
Keep it as steady as possible.
Ugh! And watch your aim!
Cream Puff Russian Roulette!
Avoid that spicy
curry bun, lovebirds!
Cream puff.
Thank heavens.
[TSUTOMU] Damn it! My "too
spicy" face is priceless!
Always fine-tuning
your comedy act.
Curry?
No, it's... it's...
way too sweet!
[SHOKO]
Okay, then.
[TSUTOMU]
On to the next one, huh?
[AKIRA]
Yep.
[MAIA]
Ugh, my teeth hurt.
You had the option of
letting me be the taster.
Yeah, right. You mean
letting you be the Savior.
Not happening today.
What do you have against
being saved? Tell me.
I dunno. It's frustrating.
Why's that?
Shush!
[MAIA]
I'm not entirely certain.
Maia! Your map!
Oh. Thanks, Karan.
[KARAN]
Jeez.
Uh. Where's Akira?
[AKIRA]
Maia!
[MAIA gasps]
Don't just wander off.
[MAIA]
You wandered off.
Where'd you go anyway?
I went to the store.
Got cash?
[MAIA]
You're charging me?
[MAIA sighs]
[AKIRA] Seriously, though,
why don't you want my help?
[MAIA]
This is a change.
Why do you give a damn
what I think all of sudden?
What happened?
[AKIRA]
I'm not really sure.
I see, so we're
in the same boat.
Could you not say that, please?
[gasps]
[MAIA]
Huh?
'Case you feel like
wandering off again.
Or you do!
[AKIRA]
Come on.
Uh. but-- Hey!
[KARAN]
Here are the current rankings.
First place: Tsutomu and Shoko!
Second place: Micchi and Yosshi!
Third: Takashi and Yumi!
Fourth: Akira and Maia!
Keep trying, Big Bro!
Hell yeah! Got this
one in the bag!
And now for the
final Trial of Love.
Find which one
is the real Nammy!
[MAIA]
Nammy?
[SHOKO] That's Namisuke's
little sister, right?
[KARAN]
You have 90 seconds to find her,
and present her trademark
flower to the judges
for a whopping 50 points!
Yeah! We do this,
we'll be in third.
Hey. You all right?
'Course.
I'm quite familiar with these
creatures' pattern of movement.
Nothin' to worry 'bout.
[whistle blows]
[CROWD cheering]
[yelling]
[KARAN] A yellow body
with a pink flower:
Nammy has cute eyelashes
and adores her brother!
Her official profile says
she's the size of a small dog,
but eyewitness reports vary,
so who's to say for sure?
It's a mystery!
I got it!
[SHOKO]
No, no! The pink flower!
Forty-five seconds
left! Good luck!
Pink flower. Pink flower.
[NAMMY giggling]
[whimpers]
I can always call for backup.
DEAVA's last line of defense!
[phone ringing]
[MAIDS]
Hua!
Damn it! They're on the clock!
Thirty seconds left!
[MAIA yelping]
The Aquaripen!
Die! Die! Die!
Fifteen seconds, guys!
[KARAN]
Ten seconds!
Nine.
Eight.
[MAIA]
Die! Die! Die! Die...
[KARAN]
Seven.
Six.
Five.
Listen to me! Respond!
[KARAN]
Four.
[MAIA]
Akira, help me!
[KARAN]
Three.
Two.
One.
Found it!
--Yeah!
--[CROWD cheering]
[SHOKO gasps]
[whistle blowing]
[KARAN]
Destiny on the Asagaya!
Unfortunately, the winners
are Tsutomu and Shoko!
What do mean "unfortunately"?
[TSUTOMU] I've dreamed of
this moment for so long.
It's so beautiful!
Shoko!
[SHOKO]
Halt.
[TSUTOMU grunts]
Uh. Yeah. My bad.
When we're in public,
we gotta play it cool.
Of course.
So, we're..?
[SHOKO giggles]
[TSUTOMU gasps]
Aw! Office romances are so in!
[MAIA] Yeah, so, toward
the end there I was a bit...
Meh. Gimme your hand.
[MAIA]
Those creatures are so menacing.
Sorry you, uh, didn't
get your crown.
'Least we had fun, right?
[MAIA]
What're you saying?
Oh dear! You've hit your head!
Let me put something
on that for you.
[MAIA]
Do you feel woozy at all?
Having trouble staying awake?
[SAKURAKO] I'm so glad
I got to be here for this!
So they were the reason
you took part in all this?
To see how they do as a couple?
I, uh...
I th-thought if I could
see it f-firsthand,
I'd be able to l-let go.
B-But it... it still...
hur... hurts.
You've changed quite
a bit, Kikogami.
Okay. Shout out to the
one you love, sweetheart!
Akira, I...
I love you!
[HAYATO] You've taken
a real step forward.
Unrequited love has its purpose.
You're beginning to understand
that. It's a good thing.
I think you're right.
[MAIA] All that and
still you rescued me.
You really are the Savior, huh?
[AKIRA]
That's not why I did it.
[MAIA]
Huh?
I just wanted to help you out.
[gasps]
[AKIRA]
Here.
Ahh! Whoa! What now?
[AKIRA]
Oh, yeah. Never mind.
[TSUTOMU]
Guys! We're headin' back!
Right. Coming.
[AKIRA]
Not now.
[growls]
Get the hell outta here!
[NESTA] When he vanishes
entirely, you'll be to blame.
[gasps]
[NESTA laughing]
[TSUTOMU]
Hey, hey, it's the singles club!
Glad you two found each other!
[HAYATO]
You seem a little.
[SAKURAKO]
Over the moon?
[TSUTOMU] Why wouldn't I be?
I've got a girlfriend!
[TSUTOMU laughing]
[AKIRA] Saviors have trouble
understanding this kinda thing.
[SAKURAKO] Someone find
me a boyfriend! Wah!
[TSUTOMU]
Next: Episode 20.
[HAYATO] "Know it!
The Reason You Were Born!"
[SAKURAKO]
Watch or you'll answer to me!