--[AKIRA] Mugen Punch!
--[MAIA] Mugen Punch!
What in the world
are you supposed to be?
I am The Savior.
[MAIA thinking]
My Verbalism Ability.
It's depleting rapidly.
Was that last attack
so exhausting?
[grunts]
[SUBETE] Damn it!
What is going on in there?
Maia! Please tell
me you're okay!
Now what?
Uh, massive gravity
distortion imminent!
Vector space is collapsing!
Because they
defeated the kanji?
Retrieve Aquarion! Immediately!
[SUBETE]
Not now!
Maia! Maia!
Hey!
[AKIRA]
My left pocket.
[gasps]
[MALE SECURITY 1A]
Cute. Move.
[SOUGON]
In times past,
humanity was at one
with the world of truth,
but the written word,
for all we prospered from it,
wrought incalculable suffering.
[SAKURAKO]
I apologize for all the noise.
Did you get decent sleep?
[SAKURAKO] Asagaya North
High School, Second Year:
Akira Kaibuki.
[SAKURAKO]
Okay, well.
There's quite a bit to
get you up to speed on.
[AKIRA]
I know.
And I know you people
need my power.
Hey! This door was
supposed to be locked!
And weren't you handcuffed?
[AKIRA]
Don't worry about it.
[SAKURAKO]
Hold on a sec!
[MAIA]
Wait, I want to speak with you.
[SAKURAKO] Looks like
someone's finally awake.
[MAIA] What are
your intentions with me?
No need to look
so terrified, young lady.
It's not as though
we plan on eating you.
I should certainly hope not!
Do you people
practice cannibalism?
Well, let me assure you,
pickled or stir fried,
I taste disgusting!
Uh, I was making a joke.
I'd like to be
executed, please.
I I will not be a burden
to Master Sougon.
It's much better
that I should die.
Sorry. I'm afraid DEAVA's just
not that kind of organization.
[MAIA]
You're a gathering of fools
who fail to
comprehend his vison!
People like you sicken me!
[SAKURAKO]
What do you mean "vision?"
[MAIA] The Master seeks
to liberate humanity
from the shackles thrust
upon it by language.
To create a world in which
people are truly connected.
His vision is a utopian ideal!
And what of the people who must
be sacrificed for that ideal?
Is his Utopia worth their lives?
Human sacrifice is inevitable!
Master says great
causes are worth any price!
[AKIRA]
Master this, Master that.
You sound like a sheep.
Oh, really?
I'll have you know:
had you not interfered,
this "sheep" would
have succeeded in--
Who're you speaking for?
You or Sougon?
'Til you find your own voice,
you're no more than his puppet.
I will not be mocked!
I'll be conducting your
interrogation personally
in a little while.
I suggest you be forthcoming.
I'd rather not get rough.
[TSUTOMU]
Seriously? A savior?
Gimme a break the guy's a nut.
No one talks like
that not in real life.
[HAYATO]
Obviously, he hijacked a vector
and charged into battle.
Not something
a sane person does.
M-Maybe not,
b-but he doesn't seem
l-like like he's a bad
p-person or anything, I guess.
And hey, we wouldn't
have been able
to take out the
M.J.B.K. without him.
I think the guy was
pretty awesome.
[HAYATO]
That's not the point.
He misappropriated DEAVA
property for his own use.
[TSUTOMU] Oy. See,
when you talk like that,
you sound like a politician.
Any way you look at it we
got our butts handed to us.
We what?
Don't get all uppity with me.
Man, D'you get up on the wrong
side of the bed this mornin'?
Are you getting' enough
calcium in your diet?
Shoko, give the man
a glass of milk, STAT.
Sorry. We don't have any.
There's mango juice,
if you want.
[HAYATO]
That's your alterative?
Like cows and mango
trees are cousins?
News flash: they're not
even remotely similar!
[TSUTOMU]
Uh-oh.
Milk Lover Hayato
is upset, everybody.
I'm... s-so sorry.
I was th-thirsty earlier
and d-d-drank what was left.
Kokone, c'mon!
The dude can only
survive our atmosphere
for three seconds
without milk in his system!
That's why we call
him The Milkman!
You can please not spread
that around, thank you!
M-M-Milkman.
D-- D-Don't die.
I can run out and
buy some more in time
for your memorial service.
[HAYATO]
Will you all stop?
Stop crying.
[AKIRA] He's right.
You've nothing to fear.
If you need saving, call me.
[KOKONE]
Wh... Wh-What was that?
[TSUTOMU]
It's him! Savior Guy!
Hey, Commander, why is he here?
It's... a long story.
[KENTO sneezes loudly]
Coming down with a cold?
Maybe?
[SAKURAKO] DEAVA. That's the
name our organization goes by.
Let me start by
telling you exactly who
and what we're up against.
We fight words capable
of devouring other words.
Creatures we've
termed: M.J.B.K.'s...
There is another dimension
where the origins of language
exist as discrete entities.
The Logos World.
This is a place where
kanji have gone rogue,
creating space around themselves
and devouring wayward concepts.
[SAKURAKO] When these
M.J.B.K. are generated,
the effects aren't confined
to the Logos World.
At first, the word
associated with it erodes.
Next, phenomena related to the
concept begin to warp reality.
Yesterday's M.J.B.K. was
born of the kanji for "twist."
As a result, things twisted or,
conversely, refused to.
[AKIRA]
Words themselves are not evil.
They only cause harm
when given voice.
Malice springs from intent.
From the will of the people.
So, spill.
Someone is clearly
making these kanji go rogue.
[SAKURAKO]
Yes. Exactly.
[SAKURAKO] Our enemy erodes the
hollowed-out meanings of words,
transforming them into M.J.B.K.
In point of fact,
he is the CEO of the social
networking service, Nesta.
You may have heard of him:
Sougon Kenzaki.
Sougon.
So if we know who the guy is,
explain to me why we're
not storming his compound?
She's told us this before.
Sougon can't be
dealt with directly
for a variety of reasons.
Subdue the man, and there's
still the issue of the M.J.B.K.
we've already lost.
They're like a cancer.
An inoperable tumor.
Once they've
consumed their word,
an M.J.B.K. erupts from Logos
Space and spreads like a virus,
consuming every word
in its path indiscriminately.
[SAKURAKO] The only weapons
capable of stopping them
before every concept in
existence is devoured
are Vectors. Ships able
to navigate the Logos World.
[HAYATO]
And they form Aquarion.
Right!
And the only people
who can pilot Aquarion
are those of us with Verbalism.
The... V-Verbalism Club.
Th-That's us.
[SAKURAKO]
Akira Kaibuki,
your instincts for
Verbalism are profound.
You possess an
enormously rare gift.
With that in mind,
I'd like to ask you
to join us here at DEAVA.
[AKIRA]
Yes. Done.
[TSUTOMU]
That was quick.
[SAKURAKO]
We call ourselves a "club,"
but what we do is
anything but child's play.
You must be fully prepared
to put your life
on the line in battle.
[AKIRA]
If the world's in danger,
I won't hesitate to fight.
I am The Savior. It's what I do.
Great. But thank you.
[TSUTOMU]
This guy's a weirdo.
[MAIA screams]
Aaaah! No!
No!
[MALE SECURITY 2A]
What's going on?
[fighting sounds]
[MAIA] I'm surprised
they actually fell for it.
S'whatcha get with volunteers.
[MAIA]
There it is. Excellent.
What do I do? Kill them?
I don't think I can take
out that many people
in one fell swoop.
And what are
they doing, exactly?
Such elegant,
choreographed movements.
A first class army
isn't this coordinated.
[MAIA] Can it be?
These women are clearly
the final guardians
of this base!
[CLEANING LADIES]
Hah!
What to do?
Facing them alone would
be a very foolish move.
C'mon, think!
[HEAD CLEANING LADY 2A]
Excuse me.
[gasps]
[MAIA]
She sensed my presence!
You must be new.
We don't tolerate loafing.
Come on, put your
back into it, hun!
You're not an old woman!
Yes, ma'am!
Right away, ma'am!
[MAIA] Be vigilant for the
right moment to sneak onboard.
Ow!
Best get that pretty little
head out of the clouds.
Less day dreamin', more work.
I beg forgiveness, ma'am!
[MAIA]
Dang. She's good.
[HEAD CLEANING LADY sneezes]
Uh oh, boss, you sick?
[HEAD CLEANING LADY 2A]
Must be making the rounds.
[sneezes]
[SUBETE]
But, why? Please!
You have to let me launch!
[SOUGON]
After that shameful display?
You damaged your vector.
What right have you to expect
I'll allow you to fly again?
But, I... I have to save Maia!
[SOUGON] I don't have time
for your infantile tantrums.
Goodbye.
[SUBETE]
Wait! Dad!
Verbalize.
[SOUGON]
Take me back to the office.
Something's come up.
[KENTO coughs]
[groans]
[TSUTOMU] Hey, man.
They give you that?
Probably not a good idea to show
it off during business hours.
Wait. What are you doing?
Ah. Guess that sorta
thing's important, huh?
Why isn't Kokone here?
Where is she?
[OKAZAKI]
And what about Hayato? Ugh!
Well, uh, Kokone had
to help out at home.
And Hayato has a part time job.
It's terrible!
We're totally swamped!
It's awright, Shoko! Fight!
And where does the
manager think she's going?
Nowhere.
Um... hon?
Yeah, I need to interrogate
our "special guest."
Oh ho, I don't think so, ma'am!
Not 'til we're through the rush!
You're staying right here!
[SAKURAKO moans]
Easy. Not so rough.
Smooth motions.
That's what does it.
Right. Smooth motions.
[HEAD CLEANING LADY 2A]
Remember: No such thing
as a stain that can't be removed
with a li'l elbow grease!
[MAIA]
Roger.
Criminy! This shouldn't
take all day!
Yes. Ma'am.
[MAIA] The workload,
it's so intense.
And yet, to look at their faces.
These women...
...are far from ordinary!
All right, ladies!
Let's break for lunch!
[CLEANING LADY 2B]
What do we have today?
Let's find out. I'm starving.
[CLEANING LADY 2D]
Did anyone bring tea?
Huh? What's the matter, rookie?
You forget to bring yours?
Huh?
[HEAD CLEANING LADY 2A]
They should've handed you one
when you clocked
in this morning.
Oh, now don't
tell me you lost it!
Uh, actually, I...
Hmm. Poor girl.
Doesn't have a clue. All right.
Come 'ere.
[CLEANING LADY 2A]
We can do better than that.
She's a growing woman.
[CLEANING LADY 2B]
Here, take this.
[CLEANING LADY 2C] I don't
much care for these anyway.
[CLEANING LADY 2D]
Fine. Eat up.
Go on. Stuff your face.
Delicious!
[HEAD CLEANING LADY 2A]
I'll bet.
[CLEANING LADY 2A] Shirobaco
lunch boxes hit the spot
during a hard day's work.
[CLEANING LADY 2C]
You ain't kiddin'!
Well, ladies what
are we waiting for?
Let's eat.
[MAIA]
Four simple rooms.
And the corridor
connecting them.
That was all.
That was my entire world.
[SOUGON]
Maia.
The outside world is a place
rife with tragedy and suffering.
Mankind languishes
in the depths of despair.
Do you understand why?
[MAIA]
Yes, Master Sougon.
Because they are captives
in a world infested with words.
Yes. Very much so.
That's why abolishing words
from this world is
the key to our salvation.
They are the enemy
of true communication.
[HEAD CLEANING LADY 2A]
Wipe your chin.
Y'got some sauce on it.
[CLEANING LADY 2A]
Don't you dare!
That's one of my dust cloths!
[laughter]
[MAIA]
Master Sougon. Forgive me.
I cannot imagine these women
to be in the depths of despair.
[SOUGON]
Verbalize. Rejoice.
Today I deign to set you free!
[M.J.B.K. ILLNESS]
Byoooooooou!
[groaning, grunting]
[SHOKO]
Kento! He's burning up!
That was quick!
They're here.
DEAVA System, activate!
Rescue team: transfer
the afflicted immediately!
[SHOKO] Contact the nearest ER,
let them know you're en route.
[SHOKO] I've gotten in touch
with Hayato and Kokone.
They're on their way.
[FEMALE OPERATOR 1A]
Confirmed.
They're inbound.
A lot of people were sick today.
Is this an M.J.B.K.?
Yes. Likely the
kanji for "fever"
has become hollow
and is running amok.
Unless we act quickly, the
damage will be exponential.
We need our star pilots.
Uh, speaking of which,
anyone seen "Savior"?
Sorry!
It's gonna take time!
We need to make
extensive repairs!
Hayato's and Tsutomu's vectors
were badly banged up, y'know!
[coughing]
This feeling.
Is it an M.J.B.K.?
And what of the people who must
be sacrificed for that ideal?
Is his Utopia worth their lives?
I can't. This can't be!
[TSUTOMU]
Ease up, man!
What good's it gonna
do you to go alone?
Oh, hey. It's that
cute enemy girl.
I gotta do
that thing I do.
By my will.
[AKIRA]
Handle these people for me?
[TSUTOMU]
C'mon, wait! You're killin' me!
[AKIRA]
Verbalize.
[M.J.B.K. ILLNESS]
Byou.
[SHOKO]
What the...? Is that fog?
[MAIA]
Please. What should I do?
Master Sougon.
No more than his puppet.
[gasps]
[MAIA]
No! My voice is my own!
[M.J.B.K. ILLNESS]
Byou.
Byou!
[MAIA]
I... I am!
[grunts]
[SHOKO] Rear propulsion balancer
functionality dropping.
He's gonna crash any second!
Ugh! Kaibuki,
pull back now!
[AKIRA]
I don't need to.
[SAKURAKO]
You can't do this alone!
[AKIRA]
I'm not.
If my master's vision
involves a world
where people truly
understand one another.
Then M.J.B.K.'s are a
betrayal of that vision!
They're a grave error!
I am loyal!
Even now I serve Master Sougon's
vision for a better world!
If he would abolish suffering.
I will do everything in my power
to protect these people!
[AKIRA] You're late.
What took you so long?
Ugh! Do not give me attitude!
That was your
own voice just now.
[MAIA]
Huh?
It's kind of nice.
C'mon! Gimme a hand!
Verbalize Merge. Now shout!
Aquariooooooon!
[AKIRA, MAIA]
Kou!
[AKIRA]
We have one soul, one body.
When the soul is healthy,
the body follows suit
and finds balance.
To treat illness,
treat the soul!
Yes! Let there be light!
[AKIRA, MAIA]
Shine!
[M.J.B.K. ILLNESS]
Byo... ou...
[groans]
[TSUTOMU]
Whoa! Okay?
Right!
Everyone up, time
for the afternoon shift!
Come on, girls!
We don't have time to sleep!
Let's get back to work!
Yeah!
[pants]
[TANAKA]
Uh, hey Kokone?
Oh. Are... Are you...
Are you okay?
Long as you're in our corner,
we've got the energy of
at least a thousand men!
Akira did this?
You're kidding.
[SHOKO]
It's so bright!
[SAKURAKO] They called
back the power of the word
with their voice.
Darkness was banished by light!
They don't just
possess Verbalism.
They were chosen by it!
[gasps]
I have to go back.
Master Sougon will be waiting.
[MAIA]
What is this?
[SOUGON]
Maia.
[MAIA]
Master Sougon! Yes! It's me!
I shall return
to your side at once!
[SOUGON]
There is no need.
[MAIA]
Huh?
[SOUGON] It is my will
that you remain there.
Monitor the pilot of
the red vector closely.
[gasps]
Hello there!
Today we girls handle
the next episode preview!
No offense, manager, but
you're too old to be a "girl."
That was totally uncalled for!
I'm cutting your pay,
effective immediately!
Then you can find
yourself another waitress!
Not a problem!
I'll just have Kokone
pick up your shifts!
If I work hard, I can
b-be a manager, too!
Look who's got ambition!
[SHOKO]
Episode Three...
[KOKONE]
"Resound! A Dream for me Alone."