[SHOKO]
The Verbalism Ability emanating
from the black Aquarion
unit is insanely high!
But these sensor readings,
are radically different
from Akira's. It's strange.
A different kind of energy?
Is that what drew in the
M.J.B.K., and revitalized them?
So you're still alive, Subete.
[SUBETE] It's just
flooding out on its own.
I don't quite have it
fully under my control.
We're going.
I'm with you.
[AKIRA]
Verbalize.
Genesis Merge. Shout it!
[BOTH]
Aquarion!
[AKIRA, MAIA]
Kou!
I know it's you, Subete!
[SUBETE]
Wall.
Quick.
Maia!
Can you see it?
The answer your son has chosen?
The decision your son
has made... for himself?
[SOUGON]
In times past,
humanity was at one
with the world of truth,
but the written word, for
all we prospered from it,
wrought incalculable suffering.
[MAO] In this new
era of globalization,
the internet has become
an indispensible tool.
I'll make a prediction.
In the not too distant future,
communication between people
will become nearly impossible
without the aid of
this emerging tech.
The brave new world
ushered in by the internet
instantly connects people
across thousands of miles.
This breakthrough
will revolutionize
our current business and take
us into the new millennium!
[HAYASHI] It was 22 years
ago, when CEO Mao Hayashi,
with assistance from
her technical adviser,
Sougon Kenzaki,
established Japan's first
network management company,
called Nesta.
The internet, now a major
aspect of everyday life,
was originally brought
to this country by Nesta.
And as their
infrastructure developed.
Nesta succeeded in rapidly
expanding their business.
Can't believe it's
been five years.
Over that time, Nesta has
grown into one of the world's
leading companies, just like
you always said we would.
All due to your ability
to explain the importance
of the network to our
potential investors.
I'd never've gotten
this far alone.
It just proves to me that making
you the company president
was the right decision.
The whole world can
start fresh from here.
As the network
continues to develop,
communication density
will increase accordingly.
Which means your dream
can come to fruition.
Your vision to reestablish the
nearly forgotten world of truth.
Until 12 thousand years ago,
the world of truth had long
existed adjacent to our own.
By merely touching it, people
were able to make the rain fall,
just by wishing it so.
Or with a request for wind,
they could summon a typhoon.
Put plainly,
it was the power to materialize
their thoughts and feelings.
Those wishes coaxed the
phenomena across to our world.
They could make magic.
[SOUGON] And the baby
that will be the key
to realizing that dream-like
world will be born tomorrow,
according to the prophecy.
Do you honestly believe in that?
That a child is to be born
chosen by Verbalism?
But exploiting a miracle
to skip straight to results?
That feels like cheating.
As communication
continues to develop,
the world of truth will
reappear eventually.
Why isn't that enough?
The development of Communication
and the chosen one's coming,
I believe both are
necessary to achieve success.
[MAO]
No, you misunderstand me.
In what way?
[MAO]
Having your fate determined
before you've even been born?
What a truly sad life.
So then, that's her stance.
For better or worse,
Mao is very human.
Well, too bad her brother's
such an inhuman monster.
[DOCTOR]
Normally, I would never abuse
a patient's privacy
like I'm about to.
But a boy was born
earlier today,
at the precise time
you said he would be.
How could you have known that?
[HAYASHI]
From what we had been told,
the mother died
from complications
shortly after giving birth,
and the child had
no other relatives.
It felt like everything was
following the whim of fate.
I know. Your name
will be Subete.
A perfect name for the
child who lost everything
the moment he was
thrust into this world.
But, you know, not having a
thing you can call your own,
only means that you've
everything to gain.
It is my hope that over
the course of your life,
you will gain everything
you could want.
May you be the master
of your own destiny.
May you chase love, dreams,
and all that is good.
Your name means "everything."
I see.
[HAYASHI] Even after adopting
the orphaned Subete,
Sougon never married Mao.
Sougon saw Subete as a tool
to reach the World of
Truth he had yearned for.
Meanwhile, Mao wanted
him to live freely,
as a normal human child.
The stark difference in
their views may have created
the invisible wall
that separated them
from that point on.
Eventually, Sougon
and I delegated
all of Nesta's
management to my sister.
The two of us were
heading overseas
to excavate and study ruins.
We needed to gain a
deeper understanding
of written culture, otherwise,
we would never stand a chance
of recreating the
World of Truth.
[SOUGON] "Dear Mao, are
you and Subete both well?
I'm getting along
fine over here.
We recently excavated a relic
from an as-yet unknown
ancient writing culture.
If we succeed in
deciphering their script,
it should prove a
valuable resource for us.
I'd very much like
to hear your voice.
I hope you'll answer your
phone when you have the time."
[MAO]
"Good morning. We're both busy,
and there's the time zone
difference to consider,
so email probably works
best for both of us.
I'm doing well. Work is hectic,
but I'm giving it my best.
I'm holding up fine, so
don't worry about me."
[SOUGON]
"It's so good to hear from you!
I'm not remotely concerned
about the company.
I know you're doing a
terrific job as president."
[SUBETE crying]
[WORKER A]
We found something!
Writing? A book?
We found this
here as well, sirs.
[MAO]
"Sorry for the late reply.
I have a lot of
complicated work to do,
so it's been hard to find time.
Don't worry about me. I'm fine."
What's the word?
Have you made any progress
in deciphering this tome?
Not yet, but there's
a lot of material here.
Whatever's written in it
must've been of great
importance to its civilization.
It's going on two years
since we left Japan.
I bet you miss your family
quite a lot by now.
Maybe Mao was right
about this whole thing.
[SOUGON]
There was no need to rush.
We shouldn't tie this
child down with fate.
Thanks to the power
of the network,
the entire world will
eventually reach the truth.
It may take years to
come about, but it will.
I see.
Mr. Kenzaki! Madame
President, she's--!
She's what?!
[IIDA] She was speeding away,
trying to shake a journalist,
but then she lost control.
The car collided
with a noise barrier.
This is all lies!
The country was focused
on Nesta's rapid growth.
They believe the
network we built
is a resource
worth nationalizing.
But that's just a smoke screen
for a government takeover.
I'm sorry. Ever since
you left the country,
they've been waiting
for an opportunity.
But the president utterly
refused to cave in,
so they used the media.
They began attacking her
character, smearing her name.
It left her feeling
alone and cornered.
I wonder if she really lost
control or if she chose--
[SOUGON yells]
Why did no one tell
me any of this?!
President Hayashi
ordered me to stay silent.
She said she didn't wanna
get in the way of your work.
[HAYASHI] Subete was
miraculously untouched,
despite being in the car
at the time of the accident.
She must have given her life
protecting Subete from harm.
[SUBETE crying]
It's a lie.
Communication? How is this
a bond between people?
[SOUGON]
I didn't understand.
It makes no sense!
[SUBETE cyring]
[screaming]
I reject it all!
Society,
built on written language which
so easily tramples our feelings!
I hate it!
Civilization is infested with
writing and devoid of heart.
And so, I vow to destroy it.
[NESTA] The power of
truth is in your hands.
[screaming]
Sougon, what's wrong?
[SOUGON] So that's how
it was. I understand now.
[HAYASHI] When he at last took
hold of the Book of Verbalism,
a wave of long dead knowledge
flooded into his being.
The destruction of
the modern world.
Only that sacrifice can
resurrect the World of Truth.
[SUBETE crying]
Don't cry.
You are the chosen one, boy,
and you'll bring about
great change in this world.
[SUBETE]
My father's recognition.
That meant everything
to me back then.
Dad! Please don't go!
[SUBETE]
I had no mother. She was gone.
My father was all I had left.
And yet, I couldn't even
get him to look at me.
It's not because you've
done anything wrong.
It's just... whenever
he looks at your face,
it brings back a wave
of painful memories.
Want some?
[SUBETE]
I felt totally lost.
I couldn't understand what
Hayashi tried to tell me.
[SUBETE]
I was becoming desperate.
If I could only
do what dad asked,
I believed it would finally
make him look my way.
Nothing again.
That's another failed attempt.
All right, take the equipment
down for recalibration!
Father, did you
come to visit me?
You were clearly
never the chosen one.
You are a failure. I have
found replacements.
I can create someone
compatible from among them.
I no longer need you,
it would seem.
[SUBETE]
Far away.
It felt like he was going
beyond the horizon,
where I couldn't reach him.
[SUBETE]
You're wrong!
I can do it!
I won't let you down, Father!
I am the chosen one!
He's doing it.
It's here!
Connection successful!
[SUBETE] I thought this
would get his attention.
[SUBETE]
But...
Even after that, my father
never looked at me.
Not even once.
[SUBETE]
Father!
Protect my son from debris.
You don't have the Book of
Verbalism. How'd you do that?
I no longer have need of it.
After all, you truly are
the chosen one, Subete.
Are you kidding me?
It's a bit late for that.
You were convinced Akira
Kaibuki was the chosen one.
You never show the true
depths of your power
until you're on your
last chance, my boy.
Same bad habit
you've always had.
But I--
Go now!
[SUBETE]
Father, wait! Come with me!
[SOUGON]
I'm finished, Subete.
Let me go to where
she's waiting.
What're saying, Father?
I don't understand!
Father!
[HAYASHI] Hey. Rise
and shine, sleepy head.
Hayashi? But how?
I was just walking along,
then you suddenly
appeared in front of me.
Honestly,
I have no clue how you made
it back from the Logos World.
I think I know.
But my father... he's gone.
Can you stand?
Then follow me.
[HAYASHI] You were still
so young at the time,
I wasn't sure if you'd
remember coming here.
This way.
[SUBETE]
Father?
Every single year
on your birthday,
your father would come to
your mother's grave here
and leave her a letter.
This year was no different.
[SOUGON]
"Dear Mao,
it's that time of
year once again.
Subete is now 17 years old.
He's grown to be
a fine young man."
[SOUGON]
"But today,
I have something to
apologize to you for.
I lied to our boy."
This power's like
nothing I've ever seen!
Fear not! Our fist
will bash through!
[SOUGON] "In order to
stimulate Subete's growth
and unlock his true
potential, I lied to him.
I told him the enemy
he now confronts
is the true chosen one."
[AKIRA, MAIA]
Mugen Punch!
[SOUGON] "I believe that
the boy has only begun
to find his strength.
But at the same time, I have
also realized my own misgivings.
You said it yourself, Mao,
you wanted the
boy to live freely,
to hold firm to his love and his
dreams, to live by his own will.
If Subete can deny the
fate thrust upon him,
then he may be able to live
freely of his own volition.
I want to see him walk
that path in life as well.
I've come to think like you now,
despite everything I said."
That's why... back then...
[SUBETE screaming]
Bastard!
Energy readings spiking!
What's going on? I've
never seen this before!
This isn't ordinary
Verbalism. It must be...
[SAKURAKO]
...the Book of Verbalism?
Akira Kaibuki.
I can hear his voice,
but our comms shouldn't
be working, they're down.
[SUBETE] You called yourself
a Savior, isn't that right?
I understand all there is
to know about your voice now.
The Savior. The title that
defines your very existence.
That's why you've been looking
for me your whole life.
[SUBETE] A Savior is
someone who saves others.
For you to be your ideal self,
there must always be something
threatening the world
to give you a sense of purpose.
Stop talking.
[SUBETE]
Accept it.
Without a threat to the
world, you're nothing.
Akira.
Scorching Fire! Sun Mugen Punch!
Rejoice, Akira.
Your most heartfelt wish?
I've come to grant it!
Wishes are one of those things
a person can never leave behind.
The wishes of the departed
get washed away
with their lives,
and lost in the stream of time.
Yet still, you will live on.
Even though I lost
everything I thought I had.
[SUBETE]
No. That's wrong.
I will always have my pain.
The pain is the one thing I own.
[MAO] It is my hope that over
the course of your life,
you will gain everything
you could want.
May you be the master
of your own destiny.
May you chase love, dreams,
and all that is good.
I can choose.
I can exercise my
own will. At last!
[SUBETE] Defeating you
is everything to me!
He broke the Mugen Punch!
I'll be taking that!
[BOTH yelp]
Akira!
Subete.
[SUBETE] Now, to reduce
everything to ash.
[SUBETE]
You wanna be the Savior?
I can be the Destroyer.
[MAIA]
What's Subete doing here?
[SUBETE] Maia, you
were fabulous as always!
[MAIA]
It was no big deal, really.
[SUBETE] No way! You were
cuter than cute. Right, Akira?
[AKIRA]
Gross.
Talking to you is bad enough,
now stop touching me.
Besides, I distinctly
remember you calling Kokone
and Karan cute, too.
[MAIA]
He's an enemy.
[AKIRA]
Definitely.
[SUBETE] Uh, next,
Episode 17:
"Shatter! The One
I Must Strike Down!"
[MAIA]
Don't come back.