- Man: IF THERE'S
ANYTHING YOU WANT,
ANYTHING AT ALL,
COME TO ME.
I'M YOUR GUARDIAN ANGEL.
- ( theme music playing )
- ( cars approaching )
- HUH?
THEY'RE COMING NOW.
- ( no audio )
- HEY, SINCE WHEN DID TOYAMA
BECOME TSUJINAKA'S BOY?
- MUST HAVE BEEN RECENTLY.
- THAT'S A SURPRISE.
HE WAS A FAVORITE OF KOHAKURA,
IF YOU KNOW WHAT I MEAN.
- MAYBE HE RECEIVED
TOO MUCH FAVOR.
- ( screaming )
- ( gasping )
- MR. KOHAKURA,
ARE YOU ALL RIGHT?
- KOHAKURA, ARE YOU HURT?
- YEAH, BUT IT JUST GRAZED ME.
- HUH?  I KNOW HIM.
HE'S ONE OF MR. TSUJINAKA'S.
- HEY, SHINJI, IT LOOKS LIKE
WE LOST CONTACT
WITH TAKA THIS TIME.
- HE'S THE FOURTH ONE
IN TWO WEEKS.
THEY PROBABLY JUST
SWITCHED SIDES
OVER TO THE ORGANO OR UNION,
BUT I HEARD THERE'S
A STRANGE STORY BEHIND IT.
THE LAST GUY WHO SAID THEY SAW
TAKA WAS YUKIO.
AND YUKIO TOLD ME TWO NIGHTS
AGO
TAKA WAS WALKING UP EAST 10TH
WITH A HUGE PALE WHITE GUY
WHO LOOKED LIKE A GHOST.
- EVERYTHING'S MISSING.
- HUH?  WHAT THE HELL ARE YOU
TALKING ABOUT?  WHAT'S MISSING?
- SOME MEMBERS OF THE ORGANO
AND THE UNION
HAVE DISAPPEARED, TOO.
- HEY, SHINJI!
- SHINJI.
HEY, WAIT.  SHOULDN'T--
OH!
- Tsujinaka:
DAMN THAT KAWAMATA.
THANKS TO HIM,
WE'RE IN SERIOUS TROUBLE.
- HOWEVER...
HE SEEMED TO BE PRETTY MUCH
IN A WEAKENED CONDITION.
THERE'S NO WAY TO BE SURE
HE WAS AIMING FOR SONODA OR NOT.
- WE CAN'T GET OFF
WITH AN EXCUSE LIKE THAT.
WHEN DID WE FIRST LOSE CONTACT
WITH KAWAMATA?
- IT WAS ABOUT A WEEK AGO.
- AND DID HE STILL HAVE
HIS ARM BACK THEN?
- YES, BUT HE HAD BEEN
BEHAVING STRANGELY
EVEN BEFORE THAT,
SAYING THAT HE'D SEEN A GHOST.
- WHAT DO YOU MEAN, A GHOST?
- I'VE HEARD ABOUT
SOME SIMILAR INCIDENTS.
MEMBERS OF THE IZAKI
AND GOTO OFFICES SEEM
TO BE MISSING AS WELL.
SOME SAY THEY SAW GHOSTS
ABDUCT THOSE PEOPLE.
- I RECALL HEARING
ABOUT THE DISAPPEARANCE
OF ONE OF IZAKI'S YOUNGER MEN
AS WELL.
WHO'S SETTING
THE WHOLE THING UP?
THE UNION?
- I DON'T THINK
THEY'RE RESPONSIBLE.
- Tsujinaka:
EXPLAIN, TOYAMA.
- REMEMBER WHAT HAPPENED
IN GABE.
THERE IS THE POSSIBILITY
THAT IT IS NEITHER THE UNION
NOR THE RACAN.
- KOHAKURA.  NO, SONODA.
- HEY.
- ( gasps )
- WHERE'S ONISHI?  HE'S NOT
HANGING WITH YOU TONIGHT?
- OF COURSE, I AM TAKING
SONODA'S FEELINGS
INTO CONSIDERATION,
BUT I WANT TO INVESTIGATE
A LITTLE MORE.
YES, I WOULD APPRECIATE IT
IF YOU COULD TELL THEM.
THANK YOU FOR YOUR HELP.
TOMORROW SONODA AND KOHAKURA
ARE GOING TO VISIT
GREAT-FATHER GOTO
IN THE HOSPITAL.
I ASKED THEM TO INCONVENIENCE
THEMSELVES BY TAKING YOU ALONG.
SO PAY YOUR RESPECTS PROPERLY.
- HMM.
- YOU SHOULD GET A HAIRCUT.
I SHOULD ALSO MAKE YOU
WEAR ONE OF THESE,
BUT I DOUBT YOU'LL...
- I'LL WEAR IT.
- HMM?
- THAT THING.
THE ONE AROUND YOUR NECK.
- WAIT HERE.
I'LL BRING YOU SOME OF MINE.
- FUNNY.  I NEVER IMAGINED
THEY'D RUN INTO YOU
AT A PLACE LIKE THAT.
SO TELL ME.
ARE YOU ON AN ERRAND
FOR ONISHI?
- NOT REALLY.
- I'VE BEEN TOLD THINGS
ARE GETTING PRETTY UGLY
IN THE ORGANO THESE DAYS.
- IT'S NONE OF THE ORGANO'S
BUSINESS OR HIS,
FOR THAT MATTER,
WHERE IT IS THAT I WANT TO GO
OR WITH WHOM I WANT
TO HAVE DINNER.
- SERIOUSLY?
- UNLESS I ASSURE YOU
ABOUT THAT,
YOU'LL BE TOO AFRAID
TO HIT ON ME.
- HMM.
EVEN IF THERE
IS A CATCH,
I FEEL LIKE BEING FOOLED
BY YOU.
- ( grunts )
- HUH?
- SHINJI AND THAT WOMAN.
HAL.
- OH!
- HUH?
YOKO.
- HEY, WAIT UP.
- WASN'T THAT ENOUGH?
I HAD A GOOD TIME,
MR. LEADER OF THE RACAN.
- WHAT YOU TALKING ABOUT?
THE NIGHT'S JUST GOTTEN STARTED.
- BE CAREFUL.
DIDN'T YOU KNOW,
BUT ONISHI SOMETIMES HEARS
THE VOICE OF THE CITY.
HE'S THE MAN WHO WAS
SPECIFICALLY CHOSEN
BY THE CITY OF LUX.
THERE IS NO OTHER MAN LIKE HIM
IN THIS CITY,
BUT I'LL GIVE YOU CREDIT FOR
WISHING YOU COULD BECOME HIM.
- HEY, WHAT ARE YOU SAYING?
- I'M SAYING
THAT YOU WANNA BE
JUST LIKE HIM.
- ( electricity crackles )
- ( panting )
COME ON, GET OVER IT.
HE'S GONE NOW.
HEY, YOKO,
WILL YOU JUST LOOK AT ME?
WHY?
WHY IS HE SO SPECIAL?
( sighs, gasps )
YOKO.
- ( laughs ) YOU'LL GIVE
TOYAMA A HEART ATTACK
WHEN HE SEES
YOU LOOKING LIKE THAT.
- THAT HE WILL.
- JUST TRY YOUR BEST NOT
TO BE DISRESPECTFUL
TO GREAT FATHER GOTO.
ONISHI HAS GONE
TO SO MUCH TROUBLE--
SONODA, YOU SEE THEM?
- I KNOW.
THEY'RE TSUJINAKA'S MEN.
IT FIGURES.
THESE GUYS REALLY
WANNA START SOMETHING.
BOY, YOU KNOW WHAT TO DO.
- ( grunts )
- MOVE IT!
- ( gasps )
WHAT'S HAPPENING?
- ( gunfire )
- DAMN YOU!
ASSHOLE!
- ( panting )
- THIS WAY!
- THANKS A LOT.
I OWE YOU BIG TIME.
- IF I LET YOU GET KILLED
RIGHT NOW,
ALL HELL WILL BREAK LOOSE
INSIDE THE ORGANO.
- ( shouts )
- ( gasping )
SOUNDS LIKE ALL THE SHOOTING
HAS FINALLY STOPPED.
- IT SEEMS THAT BOY MUST
HAVE TAKEN CARE OF THE REST.
SO EVERYTHING WILL BE FINE.
- SONODA!
- I GUESS HE MUST HAVE
MISSED ONE OF THEM.
- KOHAKURA, YOUR ARM.
- I'D LIKE TO SAY
I'M ALL RIGHT,
BUT I REALLY DID GET HIT
THIS TIME.
WELL, THEN LET'S JUST PRETEND
THAT HE'S YOUR KILLER.
- KOHAKURA,
WHAT ARE YOU--
- SORRY, MR. SONODA,
BUT YOU GUESSED IT RIGHT.
- IT MAY BE
A LITTLE UNCOMFORTABLE.
REMAIN CALM AND LISTEN
TO WHAT I HAVE TO SAY.
- WHO ARE YOU?
WHAT DID YOU DO TO ME?
- HOW DO YOU FEEL?  AFRAID?
YES, I WANTED YOU
TO FEEL THAT EMOTION
BECAUSE YOU ARE
A DIFFICULT MAN TO BREAK.
THAT BORING PERSONALITY
OF YOURS
IS MAKING THIS CITY
EXTREMELY UGLY.
YET, YOU REMAIN QUITE UNAWARE
OF IT,
DESPITE THE FACT THAT YOU'RE
REQUIRED TO BE AN EGOIST.
- WHAT?
- IN LUX, EVERYONE IS ENTITLED
TO ASSERT THEMSELVES.
A HUGE COUNCIL SYSTEM LED
BY A MIND THAT LACKS
SELF-AWARENESS.
THAT IS IMPURE.
- THINGS MUST BE PURE
AND MORE ARBITRARY.
SOPHISTICATED EGOISM AND STYLE
ARE NEEDED.
CONSIDER THAT ANY MASTERPIECE
COULD BE REDUCED
TO AN ABSOLUTE FAILURE
BY HAVING ANOTHER PERSON
ADD A BRUSH STROKE
TO THE PAINTING.
HARMONIOUS ORDER
IS JUST AN ILLUSION.
LET ME SHARE WITH YOU
HOW A CITY SHOULD BE.
I WILL CHANGE THIS CITY.
TO ME, YOU ARE
A BORING HUMAN BEING.
BUT YOU STILL HAVE VALUE
AS A NECESSARY RESOURCE.
- ARE YOU TELLING ME TO BECOME
A SOLDIER OF THE CLASS?
- HMM?
YOU SAW IT?
THE WHOLE THING?
AND NOW WHAT'LL YOU DO?
IF YOU ARE NO LONGER
A STRAY DOG,
IF YOU THINK OF YOURSELF AS
A MEMBER OF THE ORGANO NOW,
YOU MUST ALWAYS REMEMBER THIS.
THIS IS THE WAY WE DO THINGS.
THAT'S WHAT THE ORGANO
IS ALL ABOUT.
SONODA FORGOT IT
AND DIED BECAUSE OF IT.
- ALL RIGHT,
THEN I'M WITH YOU.
- THEN GO TAKE TSUJINAKA'S LIFE.
TOYAMA.
GIVE HIM THE SWORD.
- ARE YOU SURE NOW?
WITH THIS YOU CAN STOP
BEING A STRAY DOG,
BUT IN RETURN,
YOU ARE GOING TO BE
COLLARED AND CHAINED.
- YOUR ORGANIZATION,
THIS UGLY HARMONY
THAT YOU'RE SO DESPERATELY
TRYING TO PROTECT
WILL CEASE TO BE.
IT'S ONLY A MATTER OF TIME.
YOU CAN PUT AN END TO IT WITH
YOUR OWN HANDS JUST AS WELL.
- YOU SHOULD NEVER
UNDERESTIMATE ME.
DESPITE HOW I MAY APPEAR NOW,
I HAVE AN EGO
OF CONSIDERABLE SIZE.
- THERE'S NO NEED TO BE SO HASTY
IN MAKING A DECISION.
THERE IS STILL TIME.
- ( footsteps )
- ( door opens and closes )
- ( sighs )
- I KNOW YOU.
YOU'RE ONE OF ONISHI'S MEN.
- I SEE.
I SCREWED UP, DIDN'T I?
- SONODA.
HE'S DEAD.
- SONODA IS DEAD,
AND NOW I WILL BE, TOO.
WHOSE PUPPETS HAVE WE BECOME?
HACKING ME UP IS NOT
GOING TO SOLVE ANYTHING.
ISN'T THERE SOMETHING ELSE
YOU SHOULD BE DOING NOW?
- WHAT I SHOULD BE
DOING NOW IS--
- IT'S NO USE TRYING
TO TALK SENSE
INTO AN EXPENDABLE UNDERLING!
( shouts )
- ( gasps )
- THEY ORGANO IS
GOING TO GO DOWN.
DO YOU STILL THINK THAT YOU--
( shouts )
- ( gasps )
- I DID AS I SHOULD.
- WHAT'S UP WITH ALL OF YOU?
WHAT'S WRONG NOW?
- SHINJI, I'VE DECIDED
TO QUIT THE RACAN.
- WHAT?
- IT'S NO GOOD STAYING HERE
ANY LONGER.
I JUST REALIZED THAT.
- YOU'RE SERIOUSLY GONNA QUIT?
- YOU SAID WE'VE ALWAYS BEEN
FREE TO DO WHATEVER WE WANTED.
SO I'M FREE TO LEAVE HERE NOW
IF I WANT.
- WAIT A MINUTE.
WHAT THE HELL HAPPENED TO YOU?
- HAL, YOU CAN'T JUST
WALK AWAY LIKE THIS.
WE'VE ALWAYS BEEN FRIENDS
FOR SO LONG.
- THINGS CAN'T REMAIN
AS THEY WERE BEFORE.
HEY, SHINJI,
THE NEXT TIME WE MEET,
I'LL HAVE CHANGED.
AND THEN, I THINK I'LL KILL YOU.
- Yoko: HAL.
- DO WHATEVER YOU WANT.
- HAL.
SHINJI, YOU'RE LETTING HIM GO?
- LET HIM BE.
- ( scoffs )
- ( theme music playing )
- ( singing in Japanese )