- Man: IF THERE'S
ANYTHING YOU WANT,
ANYTHING AT ALL,
COME TO ME.
I'M YOUR GUARDIAN ANGEL.
- ( theme music playing )
- WE WILL DESTROY
EVERY ONE OF THEM!
- ( grunts )
- ( all shouting )
- ( men grunting, groaning )
- HUH?
- I SAID I'D KILL YOU
THE NEXT TIME WE MEET.
BUT LOOKING AT YOU NOW,
YOU'RE NOT EVEN WORTH MY TIME
TO KILL.
- HEY.
YOU CAN ALWAYS FIND ME
AT THE DRAGON'S DEN.
- HMM.
- ( gunshot )
- ( panting )
- THAT'S THE LAST.
I GUESS WE MANAGED TO SURVIVE.
- NO, THIS IS JUST
THE BEGINNING.
AND WE'RE GOING TO HAVE TO
CHANGE STRATEGY.
WHEN WE GET BACK,
WE SHOULD INTEGRATE
ALL OFFICES WITH HEADQUARTERS.
- I WONDER HOW MANY ARE
STILL ALIVE.
- ( groaning )
- COME ON.
- SHINJI.
YOU KNOW, I DON'T THINK
WE SHOULD STAY HERE.
I HEARD BOTH THE ORGANO'S
AND UNION'S OFFICES
WERE CRUSHED BY THE GHOST.
MAYBE THIS PLACE WILL BE NEXT.
- THEN YOU GUYS CAN LEAVE.
- WHAT?
- GO WHEREVER YOU WANT.
THE RACAN IS FINISHED
AS OF TODAY.
- WHY?
- Yoko: SHINJI!
- YOU CAN GO TOO, YOKO.
THIS IS GOOD-BYE.
- Yoko: SHINJI.
- Kano: YOU'RE SO CRUEL.
IF YOU'RE SO CURIOUS,
WHY DON'T YOU TOUCH IT
AND MAKE SURE FOR YOURSELF?
- EXCUSE ME, SIR?
- WE'LL RESUME THIS LATER,
DEAR SISTER.
- THERE'S A DELAY IN
THE PROCUREMENT OF WEAPONS, SIR.
ALTHOUGH THE RECEIPT OF SHIPMENT
FROM GABE WAS RECORDED.
- ( paper rustling )
- IS IT POSSIBLE THAT
IT'S BEING HELD UP
AT THE CLASS HILL?
YOU MAY GO.
- YES, SIR.
- NO LUCK, SIR.
IT SEEMS THAT ALL OF
THE DOCTORS IN THE CITY
ARE UNDER THE CONTROL
OF THE CLASS.
- HOW ABOUT DR. HIROKA?
HAVE YOU HEARD ANYTHING
FROM THE MEN WE SENT THERE?
- THEY JUST CALLED IN TO REPORT
THAT WHEN THEY ARRIVED,
THEY FOUND THE DOCTOR WAS
ALREADY DEAD.
- GO AND GET DOC.
WE NEED HER.
WHAT'S THE PROGRESS ON
THE SHUT-DOWN?
- Michiko:
I THINK IT'S ALMOST FINISHED.
THEY SHOULD START
ARRIVING HERE SOON.
- ( metal clanking )
- WHAT NOW?
YOU CAME ALONE?
- THAT'S BECAUSE...
I DIDN'T COME HERE
AS ONE OF THE SHAPES.
- SHAPES?
- HAL?
IS THAT YOU?
WHAT HAPPENED TO YOUR BODY?
- OH, YEAH. I GUESS YOU HAVE A
SCORE TO SETTLE WITH ME.
- HAL, PLEASE COME BACK TO US.
WE CAN GET EVERYONE TOGETHER
LIKE BEFORE.
AND--
- IT'S TOO LATE.
NO!
THERE'S NO GOING BACK!
GET OUT OF MY SIGHT!
BOTH OF YOU!
DAMN YOU!
I'M DIFFERENT.
GET IT?
DIFFERENT FROM THE SCUM
OF THIS CITY,
DIFFERENT FROM PEOPLE,
LIKE YOU!
- ( punches landing )
- ( panting )
- I CHANGED 'CAUSE
I WANTED TO BE STRONG.
I WANTED TO BE
STRONGER THAN YOU,
SHINJI.
AND THAT MAKES ME...
FREER THAN YOU.
- SO TO BE FREE,
YOU CHOSE TO LOOK LIKE THAT?
CAN'T YOU SEE YOU
SCREWED UP YOUR LIFE, IDIOT?!
- ( growling )
- HAL, STOP!
( gasps )
- AAH!
- ( gasps )
- ( groaning )
- ( Yoko whimpering )
( screams )
- Grandmother #1: MAYBE SO.
- Grandmother #2: VERY WELL.
- Grandmother #3:
THE SOONER THE BETTER.
- IS THAT YOU, KANO?
- IT'S BEEN TOO LONG, MOTHER.
- WE WERE THINKING
IT WAS ABOUT TIME...
- THAT YOU'D COME TO SEE US.
- Kano: I CAME HERE TO HAVE
MY TOY RETURNED TO ME.
- DON'T GET CARRIED AWAY...
- WITH THE MISCHIEF THAT
YOU ARE PLANNING TO DO.
- THE COMMON PEOPLE SERVE
A PURPOSE...
- AS THE BASE OF
OUR LIVELIHOOD.
- THE TRADITIONAL
AND TIME-HONORED METHOD
OF GOVERNANCE...
- EXISTS IN HERE
FOR A REASON.
- I'M CERTAINLY AWARE OF THAT.
- ARE YOU INDEED, MY DEAR BOY?
- EVER SINCE HE WAS LITTLE...
- KANO HAS BEEN INCORRIGIBLE.
- Onishi: WITH THE SEER GONE,
WE HAVE NO CHOICE
BUT TO ACT ON
OUR OWN JUDGMENT.
- RAN HAS SEEN SOMETHING--
- SOMETHING THAT SHE CAN'T
TELL US ABOUT.
- Ran: THAT'S RIGHT.
WE'RE GOING TO SEE THEM.
ISN'T THAT EXCITING?
THERE'S NO USE
IN BEING AFRAID.
SEE?  IT'S ALREADY
BEEN DECIDED.
- Kohakura:
WHY?!  I'M NOT A SOLDIER!
I'LL BE MORE VALUABLE
TO THE ORGANIZATION
BY WORKING IN
A POSITION OF POWER,
TO HELP CONTROL THE SOLDIERS.
THERE'S ABSOLUTELY
NO REASON FOR THIS.
WHY MUST I BE REQUIRED
TO BECOME TEXHNOLYZED?!
DON'T YOU UNDERSTAND?
IT'S BY PLACING THE RIGHT MEN
IN THE RIGHT POSITIONS
THAT AN ORGANIZATION IS ABLE
TO COME TO ITS FULL STRENGTH.
IF MORE SHAPES ARE NEEDED,
THERE SHOULD BE MANY MEN
WHO ARE PHYSICALLY YOUNGER
AND MORE CAPABLE THAN I AM.
- THAT'S RUBBISH.
- ( Kohakura scoffs )
- ENOUGH.
TAKE HIM AWAY.
- ( chains clanking )
- GET OFF ME.
( groaning )
- THE ORGANO WILL SOON
CEASE TO EXIST.
AND YOU WILL ALSO CEASE
TO BE, SOONER OR LATER.
BUT I WANT YOU TO STAY ALIVE.
- I THOUGHT YOU WERE A MEMBER
OF THE ORGANO.
- TO ME, THE ORGANO IS
NOTHING MORE THAN A MEANS
TO KEEP SURVIVING.
- I WOULD HAVE BEEN DEAD BY NOW
IF IT WEREN'T FOR THE ORGANO.
SO WOULD YOU.
- BUT THE REALITY IS
THAT I'VE ALWAYS BEEN THIS WAY.
AND I CAN'T CHANGE NOW.
- YOU WANNA LIVE SO BADLY,
YOU'LL PAY ANY PRICE.
- YOU CAN'T LIVE AT ALL
UNLESS YOU PAY IN FULL.
- Kimata: SOME OF YOU MAY FEEL
THAT OUR GRAND IDEALS
ARE ABOUT TO COLLAPSE
BEFORE EVER WE REACH OUR GOALS.
HOWEVER, THAT IS FAR
FROM THE TRUTH.
THROUGH THIS BATTLE,
WE SHALL RISE UP
AS A SHINING EXAMPLE
OF DETERMINATION.
OUR SPIRIT SHALL BE
DEEPLY ETCHED INTO THE SOULS
OF THE CITIZENS OF LUX,
AND WILL CONTINUE
TO LIVE ON FOREVER.
HOWEVER, BEFORE WE GO
INTO BATTLE,
THERE IS SOMETHING
THAT I MUST CONFESS TO YOU.
- ( all gasp )
- IN MY SEARCH FOR
BODY BEYOND THE BODY,
I ONCE SOUGHT
THE SALVATION OF MIND
THROUGH TEXHNOLYZATION.
HOWEVER, IT WAS A MISTAKE.
THE REASON I FORBADE YOU
FROM BECOMING TEXHNOLYZED...
AND ASKED YOU
TO TRAIN YOUR BODIES
WAS BECAUSE TEXHNOLYZATION
ERODES A MAN'S BODY
AND HIS SOUL.
SHOULD ANY OF YOU
BE DISAPPOINTED IN ME
AND FEEL DISCOURAGED
TO FIGHT ALONGSIDE ME,
YOU'RE FREE TO
LEAVE HERE NOW.
- SHIN!  SHIN!
SEI!  KYUU!  SAI!
- Men: SHIN!  SHIN!
- Crowd: SHIN!  SHIN!
SEI!  KYUU!  SAI!
SHIN!  SHIN!
- Doc: HAVE YOU SEEN
THEIR VERSION OF TEXHNOLYZATION?
YOU CAN'T EVEN CALL IT
TEXHNOLYZATION.
IT'S LAUGHABLE THAT
THEY'RE TURNING PEOPLE
INTO MERE WEAPONS LIKE THAT.
YET MY TEXHNOLYZATION WAS
DRIVEN AWAY
BY SUCH CHILD'S PLAY.
IT SEEMS I HAVE
NOTHING LEFT NOW.
- YOU'RE A DOCTOR.
YOU CAN HELP THE INJURED.
- THERE'S NO POINT IN
TREATING INJURIES
WHEN THEY'RE ALREADY DEAD.
THE ORGANO IS FINISHED.
WHAT ARE YOU GOING TO DO?
DIE WITH ONISHI?
- AYE.
- ( grunts )
- ( shouts, groans )
- ( metal clangs )
- PARDON ME. THE UNION
HAS STARTED THEIR ATTACK.
- Doc: NO MATTER WHERE WE GO,
WE'LL ALL DIE.
SO WHERE ARE YOU
GOING TO DIE?
- I DON'T KNOW.
- YOU'RE MY MASTERPIECE.
BUT THE CLASS DOESN'T SEE
ANY VALUE
IN THE TEXHNOLYZATION
I'VE DONE TO YOU.
- YOU TOLD ME...
THAT I HAVE MY MOTHER IN HERE.
- I FORGOT ABOUT THAT.
SORRY, I LIED.
I LIED TO YOU.
ACTUALLY...
I DUMPED WHATEVER WAS
INSIDE THE CONTAINER.
YOU SEE,
THE CELLS INSIDE OF IT
WERE LONG DEAD.
- ( grunts )
- ( gasps )
- ( groaning )
- ( gasping )
FORGIVE ME.
IF I HADN'T LIED,
YOU WOULDN'T HAVE ACCEPTED
YOUR NEW LIMBS.
FORGIVE ME.
( struggled breathing )
- ( both panting )
- ( shouts )
- ( gasps )
- ( grunting )
- ( pounding on wall )
- JUST STOP.
- ( panting )
- YOU'LL BREAK IT.
- ( grunts )
- ( men shouting )
- ONISHI, YOU TOO?
- REVENGE IS SOMETHING
WE BOTH HAVE IN COMMON.
- Man: CHANCELLOR,
MORE OF THEM ARE COMING!
- KOHAKURA?
- NOT EXACTLY WHAT I WANTED,
BUT IT'S THE ONLY WAY LEFT
FOR ME TO LIVE.
- THIS BATTLE IS
COMPLETELY FUTILE.
WITHDRAW YOUR MEN.
- ONISHI, THIS IS A BATTLE
TO SHOW OUR SPIRIT.
OUR STRUGGLE IS MEANT TO INSPIRE
THE COMRADES OF THIS CITY.
- KIMATA.
- THE OPERA HOUSE
LOCATED DOWN THE ROAD
IS THEIR HEADQUARTERS.
I'M GOING TO GET THERE EVEN IF
I'M THE ONLY MAN LEFT STANDING.
- FOLLOW HIM!
- ( men shouting )
- ( grunting )
- KIMATA!
- ( groans, shouts )
- ( shudders )
RETREAT!
EVERYBODY PULL OUT.
WE HAVE A TRUCK WAITING DOWN
AT THE END OF THE ALLEY.
GET ON IT.
THAT INCLUDES UNION MEMBERS.
- ( men shouting )
SHIN!  SHIN!
SEI!  KYUU!  SAI!
- GET UP.
- WE'RE HERE.
TIME TO GO.
SHALL WE?
- ( theme music playing )
- ( singing in Japanese )