- Man: IF THERE'S
ANYTHING YOU WANT,
ANYTHING AT ALL,
COME TO ME.
I'M YOUR GUARDIAN ANGEL.
- ( theme music playing )
- ( footsteps )
- ( clanging )
- ( gunfire )
- DAMN IT.
( grunts )
- ( shouts )
- ( grunts )
- ( gasps )
- YOSHII.
IS THIS WHAT YOU
WANTED TO DO?
( grunts )
- ( clanging )
- ( piano playing )
- Doc:
THIS CITY IS FINISHED.
EVERYBODY'S GOING TO BE
TURNED INTO A FREAK LIKE THEM.
THERE'S NOWHERE TO RUN.
YOU DON'T HAVE TO
BE A HERO.
YOU'RE ANGRY WITH ME,
AREN'T YOU?
YOU CAN JUST LEAVE ME HERE.
- I MADE A PROMISE
TO ONISHI.
- WHAT DIFFERENCE
DOES IT MAKE,
FULFILLING
YOUR DUTY OR NOT?
YOU DON'T EVEN KNOW
IF HE'S STILL ALIVE.
- KEIGO ONISHI.
- THAT'S RIGHT.
I WAS WAITING FOR YOU, SEE?
( chuckles )
- ( beeping )
- IT SEEMS THAT THEY'RE
NOT ATTACKING
WOMEN AND CHILDREN.
LET'S GO.
- ( beeping continues )
- HEY, HAL?
JUST THINK ABOUT IT
FOR A SECOND.
WITH A BODY LIKE THAT,
HOW IS IT EVEN POSSIBLE
TO MAKE LOVE
TO A WOMAN?
- ( match lights )
- ( exhales )
- SHINJI?
WHERE ARE YOU GOING NOW?
- THERE'S SOMETHING
I'VE STILL GOTTA DO.
- ( humming )
- I GAVE AN ORDER TO THE PEOPLE
WHO ARE REMAINING HERE.
I TRUST YOU WILL SUFFER
NO INCONVENIENCE.
- WHY IS IT INEVITABLE
THAT YOU MUST GO?
THIS PLACE BELONGS TO
YOU AND YOUR PEOPLE.
- THAT MAY BE TRUE,
BUT WE CAN NO LONGER
AFFORD TO LOSE THE SEER.
- ( clanging )
- Kohakura: MR. KANO,
MY ARM HAS SUDDENLY
BECOME NUMB,
AND I HAVE
A SPLITTING HEADACHE.
- Kano: THAT HAPPENS WHEN
YOU ARE IN A WEAKENED
PHYSICAL CONDITION.
- I NEED A TREATMENT.
- IF GANGRENE IS ALREADY
SET INTO YOUR BRAIN,
THEN IT'S HOPELESS.
- Kohakura:
THAT CAN'T BE.
- HAVE YOU FOUND
KEIGO ONISHI YET?
- I'M SORRY,
BUT WE HAVEN'T.
- AS LONG AS HE'S ALIVE,
HE MIGHT BE ABLE TO UNITE
ALL THE SCATTERED FORCES.
IT WILL BE TROUBLESOME
IF THE IGNORANT MASSES
START SUPPORTING HIM.
- I MIGHT HAVE A PLAN, SIR.
IT'S BEEN REPORTED THAT
THE SEER IS IN THE CITY.
- THE SEER?
SHE HAS THE POWER
TO BRING TOGETHER
THE IGNORANT MASSES.
- DO YOU WANT TO
KNOW YOUR FUTURE,
MR. KOHAKURA?
- ( gasps )
YES, I DO.
- Kano: RUBBISH.
- Doc: THIS IS WHERE YOU WERE
SUPPOSED TO MEET ONISHI.
THE ORGANO
IS FINISHED NOW.
AND SO IS HE.
GIVE IT UP.
YOU'VE DONE ENOUGH
TO FULFILL YOUR DUTY.
YOU HAD NOTHING TO DO WITH
THIS WORLD FROM THE BEGINNING.
IF YOU JUST
TELL YOURSELF THAT,
IT WILL BE EASIER
TO LEAVE.
- BUT STILL...
IT'S ALL I HAVE.
- ( chuckles )
THE BOTH OF YOU
ARE COMPLETE IDIOTS.
YOU AND ONISHI.
THE ONLY THING YOU CAN TRUST
IS WHAT YOU SEE IN FRONT OF YOU.
THE ONLY WAY YOU CAN
EXPRESS ANYTHING
IS THROUGH THE ANGER
YOU HAVE AT THE MOMENT.
I WANT YOU TO
JUST HOLD ME.
I'M FEELING AFRAID,
SO PLEASE?
HARDER.
MORE.
( sighs )
THIS IS HOW MY WORK
SHOULD BE USED.
LET'S LEAVE THIS CITY.
IF WE GO TO GABE
WE MIGHT STILL BE ABLE
TO FIND A PLACE TO SURVIVE.
- AFTER ALL THIS TIME.
( gasps )
- MR. ONISHI?
- JUST GO.
GET DOWN!
- ( door slams )
- I'M SORRY.
- ( electricity humming )
- SO WHERE'S YOUR
PRETTY LITTLE SECRETARY?
I GET IT.
SO YOU WERE THINKING
THE SAME THING AS ME.
- ( door opens )
- Onishi: WHOEVER LET US IN
IS TELLING US TO PROCEED.
- Shinji: THERE'S NOTHING
SPECIAL ABOUT THIS PLACE.
- Grandmother #3: ARE WE HAVING
RAIN, THUNDER, OR WIND NOW?
- Grandmother #2: WE DON'T HAVE
ANYTHING LIKE THAT HERE.
- Grandmother #3: DID THEY WIN
AND ALSO LOSE THE WAR?
- Grandmother #1: SHH.
THE GUESTS HAVE ARRIVED.
- Grandmother #2:
YOU'VE COME TO SEE US.
- Grandmother #3: FINALLY.
- SO I GUESS IT WAS YOU.
- IT SEEMS YOU WERE
LISTENING TO OUR CONVERSATION.
- THAT'S EAVESDROPPING.
- THOSE LEGS MADE YOU DO IT.
- MY LEGS?
- Grandmother #1:
KANO HAS CHANGED.
HE'S BECOME A BIGGER FOOL.
- Grandmother #2:
ALL BECAUSE OF YOUR SORDID LEGS.
- Grandmother #1: BUT WE
MADE SURE TO PROMPTLY DUMP
THOSE LEGS OF YOURS.
- Grandmother #3: KANO HAD
NO NEED OF SUCH THINGS
FROM THE VERY BEGINNING.
- KANO?
- Grandmother #2:
YOU MUST STOP KANO'S GAME.
- Grandmother #1:
KANO'S GAME HAS GONE TOO FAR.
- Grandmother #3:
THE ONLY THING KANO WANTS
IS TO HAVE A BIGGER PLAYGROUND.
- Shinji:
A BIGGER PLAYGROUND?
WHAT DOES THAT MEAN?
HE SAID SOMETHING ABOUT
THE CLASS UNIFYING
AND RECONSTRUCTING
THE CITY.
- Grandmother #1:
HE'S BEING SELFISH.
HE JUST WANTS TO GO
BACK TO THE WORLD ABOVE
AS SOON AS HE CAN.
- Grandmother #2: AND DO
WHATEVER HE LIKES THERE.
- Grandmother #3: YOU PEOPLE ARE
NOTHING MORE THAN HIS PAWNS.
- Grandmother #1: YOU MUST
NOTIFY THE WORLD ABOVE.
- Grandmother #2:
YOU MUST SOUND THE ALARM.
- Grandmother #3:
YOUR GUIDE IS WAITING FOR YOU.
- ( Shinji chuckles )
- Onishi: SO I GUESS
YOSHII WAS RIGHT.
I WAS TOO IGNORANT.
IMAGINE THAT.
I WAS DESPERATE TRYING
TO GET TO THIS PLACE
ALL THESE YEARS.
- TOO BAD YOU LOST
YOUR LEGS FOR NOTHING.
WHAT ARE YOU GONNA DO?
ARE YOU REALLY GOING?
SORRY TO DISAPPOINT YOU,
BUT I'M NOT GOING.
I'M GONNA BE THE ONE
WHO KILLS THIS KANO GUY.
HUH?
- HMM?
- Shinji: I KNOW YOU.
I SAW YOU HANGING
AROUND WITH YOSHII.
- Kano: SO THEY SENT
ONISHI ABOVE GROUND.
I SUPPOSE THEY THINK
THEY'VE OUTWITTED ME.
THEY GAVE BIRTH TO FATHER,
MATED WITH HIM,
AND GAVE BIRTH TO ME.
I WISH I HAD TORN
THEIR WOMBS APART
WHEN I FIRST CAME OUT.
- HUH?
- Doc: SO THAT'S THE SEER.
( gasps )
THE TRAIN IS HERE.
( panting )
- ( gasps )
- HEY.
- Doc: I HAD A FEELING
IT WOULD BE SOMEWHERE WARM.
THE PLACE THAT PEOPLE
OF THE CLASS WOULD BE
ALLOWED TO
GO UP TO ONE DAY
IN THE FAR FUTURE.
BUT IT'S IMPOSSIBLE TO BELIEVE
THAT SUCH A PLACE
ACTUALLY EXISTS.
- Onishi:
DOC, GO ABOVE GROUND FOR ME,
AND TELL THEM ABOUT THE
HORRIBLE STATE OF THIS CITY
AND ABOUT KANO'S PLANS.
- Shinji: LOOKS LIKE THAT GUY
WANTS TO BE YOUR GUIDE.
- ICHISE, I WANT YOU
TO GO ALONG WITH HER.
I SUPPOSE THE PEOPLE ABOVE
WILL LISTEN TO DOC.
THAT IS, IF THEY'LL
LISTEN TO ANYONE.
BUT STILL...
IT'S THE PLACE THAT
DROVE YOSHII DOWN HERE
TO INCITE ALL THIS CHAOS.
ICHISE,
WE'VE ALL BEEN TRAPPED
IN A SMALL WORLD.
NOW WE'VE COME TO THIS.
BUT YOU'RE STILL YOUNG.
IT'S TIME FOR YOU TO GO
AND SEE MANY THINGS.
- I DON'T WANT TO GO.
I'M NOT--
- ARE YOU WORRIED
ABOUT THAT GIRL?
THE ONE WHO'S GATHERING
PEOPLE AT THE OBELISK?
- YOU MEAN THE SEER?
- Doc: WITH ALL THOSE
PEOPLE AROUND HER,
THOSE FREAKS WON'T BE
ABLE TO DO ANYTHING.
- ICHISE, AS OF NOW
YOU NO LONGER
OWE ME ANYTHING.
- ( panting )
- ( theme music playing )
- ( singing in Japanese )