- Man: IF THERE'S
ANYTHING YOU WANT,
ANYTHING AT ALL,
COME TO ME.
I'M YOUR GUARDIAN ANGEL.
- ( theme music playing )
- Doc: IT'S OPEN.
- Man on radio:
THE BIRD SINGS ON THE FINGER.
I REPEAT,
I REPEAT...
- FOR NO REASON
I ALWAYS HAD THIS THOUGHT.
I ALWAYS BELIEVED THAT
THE PEOPLE OF THE CLASS
COULD COME BACK ABOVE GROUND
IF WE WANTED TO.
BECAUSE WE'RE THE PEOPLE
WHO SHOULD BE LIVING
ABOVE GROUND BY RIGHT.
- MY JOB TO TAKE YOU HERE.
I DID IT.
I'M LEAVING.
- I THOUGHT...
IN MY INFINITE WISDOM,
THAT TEXHNOLYZATION
WAS THE VERY MEANS NEEDED
FOR MANKIND TO EVOLVE
INTO THE NEXT SPECIES.
BUT NOW...
WHILE WE WERE
STRUGGLING DESPERATELY
TO SURVIVE UNDERGROUND,
THE PEOPLE ABOVE GROUND HAD
LONG GIVEN UP ON SURVIVING.
- THIS ENTIRE PLACE,
IT'S ONLY FOR DEAD PEOPLE.
- HUH?
- THERE'S NO ONE STILL
ALIVE IN THIS PLACE.
- THEY JUST SIT COMFORTABLY
AND WAIT FOR
THE HUMAN SPECIES
TO REACH ITS FINAL END.
YOU'RE RIGHT.
THIS IS HADES.
- THAT'S IT.
I'M GOING BACK.
WHAT ABOUT YOU, DOC?
- I'M ALREADY
ONE OF THE DEAD.
- ( door closes )
- ( elevator dings )
- ( sighs )
- ( monitor beeps )
- Yoshii: MR. SAKIMURA?
- HUH?
- I HEARD YOU'RE GOING
DEEP UNDERGROUND.
I REALLY WISH I WAS.
I'VE BEEN APPLYING FOR IT
FOR A LONG TIME.
- YOSHII...
- I'LL GET THERE ONE DAY.
I'M SURE.
COME ON, MR. SAKIMURA,
WHY DIDN'T YOU DECLINE?
I THOUGHT NOBODY BUT ME
WOULD WANT TO GO UNDERGROUND.
- INITIALLY,
I DIDN'T WANT TO GO.
BUT I THOUGHT--
- ( alarm beeps )
- HUH?
- Man on radio: 38 39, 40.
I REPEAT TWICE,
38, 39, 40.
I REPEAT TWICE...
LISTEN CAREFULLY.
THE WIDOW'S VEIL
IS IN THE SUN'S LUNCH.
I REPEAT,
THE WIDOW'S VEIL...
- LOOK,
THAT'S THE CLEAREST GHOST
I'VE EVER SEEN.
- YOU GUYS ARE THE ONES
WHO ARE GHOSTS.
- THIS IS A SURPRISE.
YOU'RE ALIVE.
- WHAT ABOUT YOU?
- WELL, THAT'S A GOOD QUESTION.
IF SITTING HERE
DAY AFTER DAY
ONLY REMINISCING
ABOUT THE PAST
CAN BE CALLED LIVING,
THEN I GUESS WE ARE.
- THAT IS IF WE WHO ARE
BARELY HOLDING ONTO OUR SANITY
BY HAVING OUR GHOSTS
WALK AROUND
CAN BE CALLED LIVE HUMANS.
- Ichise: YOU WANNA DIE NOW?
- OH, MR. SAKIMURA.
YOU LOOK LIKE A COMPLETELY
DIFFERENT MAN.
IT SEEMS THAT YOU'VE
BECOME SO MUSCULAR.
- I WAS DOING PHYSICAL LABOR.
DOWN BELOW.
- HOW LUCKY FOR YOU.
WHAT KIND OF LABOR?
- TRAIN OPERATOR MOSTLY.
- I SEE.
A TRAIN OPERATOR.
- UH, SIR?
- YES?
- IT SEEMS A TRAIN
IS COMING UP FROM LUX,
THE UNDERGROUND CITY.
- DO YOU KNOW WHO'S COMING?
- PROBABLY.
A FULLY-ARMED
TEXHNOLYZED FORCE.
- OH?  WHAT ARE THEY
COMING HERE FOR?
- I THINK THEY'RE COMING
TO THE SURFACE WORLD
AS THE VANGUARD OF
THEIR ATTACK AGAINST US.
- OH, I UNDERSTAND NOW.
WELL, THANK YOU VERY MUCH
FOR THE REPORT, MR. SAKIMURA.
- ( gasps )
- WAS THERE ANYTHING ELSE?
- NO, SIR.
- WHAT'S YOUR NAME?
- ICHISE.
- AND WHAT IS YOUR
LAST NAME, YOUNG MAN?
- DON'T HAVE ONE.
- OHH.
THAT SOUNDS GOOD.
EVERY HUMAN BEING
IS ON HIS OWN.
NO POINT BEING BOUND
BY A NAME.
I SUPPOSE THAT YOUR PARENTS
MUST BE A GREAT DEAL
YOUNGER THAN ME
TO HAVE SUCH
A YOUNG SON AS YOU.
- THEY'RE LONG GONE.
BOTH MY MOTHER AND FATHER.
- YOU WON'T HAVE TO
WAIT MUCH LONGER.
BE PATIENT.
( grunts )
I'LL MAKE SOME COFFEE.
- YOU CAN'T NOW, BUT...
- HMM?  WHAT'S THAT?
- YOU SHOULD COME
TO LUX SOME DAY.
THE PEOPLE OF LUX
ARE AT LEAST ALIVE.
- YOU'RE RIGHT.
- ( sighs )
THANK YOU.
I'M GOING NOW.
- OH, YOU ARE?
ICHISE?
I JUST THOUGHT...
IF YOU WOULD
STAY HERE FOREVER...
IT WAS JUST A THOUGHT.
THE EMPTY DREAM
OF A GHOST.
- ( door opens )
( door closes )
- TAKE ME TO
THE TRAIN STATION.
- ( beeping )
- GOOD-BYE, LUX.
WHAT ARE THEY DOING?
NO, THEY CAN'T.
( murmurs )
- ( panting )
- ( gunfire )
( gasps )
- ( sighs )
THE SKY IS HIGH.
BUT IT LOOKS LIKE THAT'S
ABOUT THE ONLY DIFFERENCE.
YOU KNOW,
I JUST GOT HERE.
YOU COULD GIVE ME A MOMENT
OR TWO TO REST.
- THEN STAY.
I'M GOING BACK.
- GO BACK AND THEN DO WHAT?
IS THERE SOMEONE
WAITING FOR YOU?
( chuckles )
THAT SEER GIRL
FROM GABE PERHAPS.
SHE'S CAPTURED BY NOW.
MR. KANO WANTED HER.
- ( groans )
- ( chuckles )
MAYBE ONISHI?
I THOUGHT HE WAS
A LITTLE SMARTER
THAN HE ACTUALLY WAS.
IT SEEMS HE CRAWLED
UNDER THE OBELISK.
I'M SURE HE MUST
BE DEAD BY NOW.
- ( gunshots )
- NOW THAT THE TUNNEL
IS DESTROYED,
KANO WON'T BE ABLE
TO SEND HIS SOLDIERS
UP HERE FOR SOME TIME.
YOU AND I CAN'T
GO BACK EITHER.
- ( explosion )
- ( beeping )
- I HAVE NO HATRED
TOWARD YOU.
IN FACT,
I RATHER LIKE YOU.
THAT'S WHY I WANT TO
KILL YOU MYSELF.
- I SEE.
SAME GOES FOR ME.
- ( grunts )
- ( gasps )
- Doc on radio: I BELIEVE
WHAT ATTRACTED ME
TO ICHISE WAS HIS EYES.
THEY WERE SPECIAL.
HIS EYES ARE THE EYES
OF OUR PARENTS' PARENTS.
THE EYES THAT THE FIRST
IMMIGRANTS TO LUX ALL HAD.
REPRODUCTION.
THAT'S THE REASON THEY WERE
DRIVEN UNDERGROUND
IN THE FIRST PLACE.
I NEVER HAD ENOUGH
COURAGE TO GO THROUGH
THE PROPER TESTING,
BUT I KNEW FOR SURE
FROM EARLY ON
THAT I LIKED THE ABILITY
TO PRODUCE OFFSPRING.
IN A SENSE,
ICHISE WAS CARRYING
MY CHILD.
I WAS HOPING TO SEE
HOW MUCH POWER
ICHISE'S TEXHNOLYZED LIMBS
WOULD GAIN
FROM THE ADDITION
OF MY CELLS
CULTIVATING HIS BIO-CIRCUIT.
BUT THAT'S NO LONGER
POSSIBLE NOW.
- ( panting )
- I'M HAVING SUCH
A WONDERFUL TIME.
I FEEL SO FORTUNATE
THAT WE CAN TRY TO
KILL EACH OTHER LIKE THIS.
- ( footsteps approaching )
- ( grunts )
- ( sighs )
( grunts )
- ( grunts )
- I THANK YOU, BROTHER.
- I'M VERY GLAD
THAT I CAME.
- SO IT'S YOU.
- WE HAVE ALWAYS BEEN TOLD
THAT THE REASON YOUR PEOPLE
WERE ISOLATED UNDERGROUND
WAS TO PROTECT US,
THE THEONORMAL.
BUT NOW I SUSPECT
THERE MAY HAVE BEEN
ANOTHER REASON THAT
WASN'T TOLD TO US.
AS YOU CAN SEE,
THE THEONORMAL
ARE ON THE VERGE
OF EXTINCTION AS A SPECIES.
DESPITE OUR UPMOST EFFORTS
TO ELIMINATE DANGEROUS ELEMENTS,
WE WEREN'T ABLE TO DELAY
OR ANNIHILATION.
NO MIRACLE HAPPENED
THAT WOULD BRING US INTO
THE NEXT STEP OF EVOLUTION.
I'M STARTING TO
BELIEVE THAT MAYBE
OUR PARENTS' PARENTS GENERATION
HAD PINNED ALL THEIR
HOPES FOR SURVIVAL
UPON YOUR PEOPLE.
ALTHOUGH IT'S NOTHING MORE
THAN MY SPECULATION.
- HOW SELFISH.
OF BOTH YOU AND
YOUR PARENTS' PARENTS.
- WE DESTROYED THE STAIRCASE
AND THE AIRSHAFT.
THE PEOPLE UNDERGROUND WON'T
BE ABLE TO COME UP HERE ANYMORE.
NEITHER WILL YOU.
I KNOW IT'S
A SELFISH REQUEST,
BUT I'D LIKE YOU
TO STAY HERE.
- THE STAIRCASE IS DESTROYED,
BUT THE AIRSHAFT ITSELF
ISN'T BLOCKED.
- THAT'S GOOD ENOUGH.
- ( breathing heavily )
( gasps )
IT'S YOU.
I WANT--
I MEAN,
I HAVE TO APOLOGIZE TO YOU.
FOR A LONG TIME...
IT WAS EVER SINCE
MOTHER HAD DIED.
I ALWAYS THOUGHT
IT WAS YOU WHO KILLED HER.
I THOUGHT YOU WERE CORRUPTED
BY WORTHLESS THINGS LIKE MONEY.
I NEVER THOUGHT...
I NEVER EVEN IMAGINED THAT
YOU COULD HAVE BEEN FRAMED
BY SOME FILTHY BASTARDS.
I'M VERY SORRY...
FATHER.
- ( theme music playing )
- ( singing in Japanese )