- Man: IF THERE'S
ANYTHING YOU WANT,
ANYTHING AT ALL,
COME TO ME.
I'M YOUR GUARDIAN ANGEL.
- ( theme music playing )
- TAKING AN ASSESSMENT
OF THE DAMAGE IS NOW SECONDARY.
POINT IS SOMEONE MUST
TAKE THE BLAME.
SADLY, THERE SEEMS TO BE
NO OTHER WAY AROUND IT.
- IF WE FAIL TO SHOW OUR
SINCERITY TO THE CLASS,
IT'LL ALMOST CERTAINLY
AFFECT OUR FUTURE.
- WE THINK THE ONLY SOLUTION
IS A CHANGE OF LEADERSHIP.
- WE MUST DO SOMETHING NOW.
- IN MY HUMBLE OPINION,
IT'S SIMPLY A MATTER OF MAKING
A CLEAR DISTINCTION
BETWEEN THOSE
WHO DIDN'T DO WHAT THEY WERE
SUPPOSED TO DO
AND THOSE WHO DID.
- BUT AFTER THAT I PUT OFF
A FINAL DECISION.
SO YOU'RE UNDER MY PROTECTION
FOR THE TIME BEING.
- I'M SORRY FOR CAUSING YOU
SO MUCH TROUBLE.
- DON'T APOLOGIZE.
DID YOU DO ANYTHING
YOU MUST APOLOGIZE FOR?
IT'S FOR THE BEST
THAT YOU LAY LOW
FOR THE TIME BEING.
WHATEVER HAPPENS HAPPENS
FOR BOTH THE CITY
AND THE ORGANIZATION.
- YES.
- YOU SEEM TO BE CONCERNED
ABOUT THAT BOY.
- SIR.
- ( laughs )
WELL, WHATEVER HAPPENS,
HAPPENS FOR HIM AS WELL.
- WE'RE GOING TO BE BUSY.
- SIR.
- I DON'T THINK WE SHOULD
WAIT UNTIL I BECOME LEADER.
WE NEED TO START DOING
THE THINGS WE CAN RIGHT NOW.
- AH.
- DON'T "AH" ME.
HERE'S A PIECE OF ADVICE.
A COMPETENT MAN IS ONE
WHO ALWAYS THINKS AHEAD.
UNDERSTAND?
- UH, YEAH.
- HE TELLS ME THAT YOU SEEM
TO BE BORED.
SO I THOUGHT YOU COULD KILL
SOME TIME BY GOING WITH US.
THERE'S SOMEONE I WANT YOU
TO FIND.
HE'S USUALLY HANGING AROUND
IN THIS AREA,
BUT HASN'T BEEN SEEN
FOR QUITE A WHILE.
I CAN SEE YOU HAVE
NO PARTICULAR OBJECTION.
YOU JUST HAVE TO GIVE HIM
A LITTLE HAND WITH IT.
THAT'S ALL I'M ASKING.
- HUH.
INTERESTING.
YOU'VE HEARD THE SAYING,
"BIRDS OF A FEATHER
FLOCK TOGETHER."
( laughs )
- Toyama: THE ORGANO IS MADE UP
OF A FEW ORGANIZATIONS
UNITED AS ONE.
THIS UNITY WOULDN'T HAVE
BEEN POSSIBLE
UNDER ORDINARY CIRCUMSTANCES.
IT EXISTS ONLY BECAUSE A MAN
LIKE MR. ONISHI IS IN CHARGE.
I SEE YOU'RE NOT
VERY INTERESTED.
DID YOU WAIT LONG?
- THANKS TO YOU
I'M DRUNK IN BROAD DAYLIGHT.
- SO--
- NO DOUBT IT WAS SAKAZAKI.
A WITNESS SAW HIM CARRYING
A PAPER BAG
AND WALKING HURRIEDLY PAST
THE OBELISK
ON THE DAY IT GOT BLASTED.
- AND?
- MMM.
THEN HE STARTS SPENDING
ALL OF HIS MONEY
LIKE THERE'S NO TOMORROW
AND THEN JUST DISAPPEARS.
WHERE DO YOU THINK HE WENT?
OVER TO MASAMUNE'S FACTORY.
MOST LIKELY HE GOT ATTRACTED
TO THE BOOZE THERE.
CHANCES ARE HE SHOULD STILL
BE SLUMMING AROUND IN THAT AREA.
WHAT DO YOU SAY?
IF YOU DON'T WANNA GO, I CAN
ARRANGE SOMEONE TO GO FOR YOU.
BUT THEN I'M GONNA NEED
A LOT MORE OF THIS.
- I'LL GO.
- WHATEVER.
I THINK THE CHANCES ARE PRETTY
GOOD THAT HE WON'T KILL YOU
IN COLD BLOOD.
- UH-HUH.
- LOOK, WE ALL KNOW THAT
THE ARSONISTS WERE A FEW IDIOTS
IN OUR ORGANIZATION,
BUT I HAVE ONISHI'S WORD
THAT YOU'LL BE COMPENSATED.
AND NO MATTER WHAT HAPPENS
IN OUR END OF THINGS,
YOU'LL HAVE MY COMPLETE SUPPORT.
- ( all gasp )
- YOU DO UNDERSTAND WHAT I MEAN.
I'M SURE YOU DO.
WELL, I'LL COME AND SEE
YOU AGAIN SOME TIME,
AND I'M SURE WE CAN CONTINUE
THIS LITTLE CHAT THEN.
IN THE MEANTIME,
PLEASE WAIT UNTIL
YOU RECEIVE FURTHER DIRECTION
FROM US.  UNTIL THEN.
- SO DID IT LOOK LIKE
I'M IN CHARGE?
- I THINK SO.
- WHO WAS THAT?
- WELL, MUST BE SOME PISS ANT.
- WHATEVER HAPPENS, PLEASE TRY
TO CONTAIN YOURSELF.
THIS IS THE KIND OF PLACE
THAT EVEN RESIDENTS
DO THEIR BEST TO STAY AWAY FROM.
- ( gasps )
- IS MY OLD MAN HERE?
- YES.
- WELL, LOOK WHO'S HERE.
- I DON'T KNOW.
- THERE IS NO WAY
YOU DON'T KNOW.
- THEN I FORGOT.
( sighs ) BUT WHO KNOWS?
MAYBE I'LL REMEMBER IT
SOONER OR LATER.
- DON'T EVEN THINK ABOUT IT.
THIS MAN IS UNDER THE PROTECTION
OF ONISHI.
- AND HERE I WAS THINKING
YOU MIGHT HAVE MATURED A BIT.
- MEANING?
- YOU'VE MADE A MISTAKE
IF YOU THINK I'LL GIVE YOU
THE INFORMATION
BECAUSE I'M YOUR FATHER.
THE WORLD DOESN'T
REVOLVE AROUND YOU.
YOU'VE LOST YOUR SENSE
OF RIGHT AND WRONG.
THAT'S WHAT HAPPENS WHEN YOU
JOIN A GROUP LIKE THE ORGANO.
DON'T COME HERE EMPTY-HANDED
LIKE A LITTLE BRAT.
IF YOU WANT SOMETHING FROM ME,
THEN YOU HAVE TO PAY THE PRICE.
IF YOU CAN'T,
THEN GET OUT OF MY SIGHT.
- WHAT DO YOU WANT?
- YOU KNOW WHAT I WANT.
- IF YOU WEREN'T MY FATHER,
I'D HAVE ALREADY KILLED YOU.
- HMM.
- COULD YOU PLEASE WAIT OUTSIDE
FOR ME?
- Man: RAN, AREN'T YOU
GOING TO THE CITY?
THE FLOWERS YOU PICKED
ARE GOING TO WITHER AWAY.
- NOTHING.
NOTHING EVER CHANGES.
- RAN.
- Toyama:
IS THE INFORMATION SOLID?
- YEAH,
BUT THE BOSS THERE
CAN BE SUCH A PIGHEAD.
WHETHER YOU CAN SEE SAKAZAKI
OR NOT WILL DEPEND
ON HOW WELL YOU DO.
BUT I THOUGHT YOU WERE
PRETTY GOOD.
- NEXT TIME I REALLY
WILL KILL YOU.
- AND?
- AND THAT'S ALL THERE
IS TO IT.
- BUT YOU STILL HAVEN'T
EXPLAINED WHAT IT IS.
I DON'T GET WHAT
YOU'RE TRYING TO SAY.
- YOU DON'T GET IT?  WHY NOT?
- DID YOU GET WHAT HE SAID?
- UNH-UNH.
NOT ONE SINGLE WORD.
- WELL.
- I'M TELLING YOU
THAT I'LL MAKE SURE
YOU WON'T LOSE ANYTHING
FROM IT.
- SO THEN WHY ARE YOU HERE?
- BECAUSE I'LL BE THE NEW HEAD
OF THE ORGANO.
- Both: HUH?
- GET LOST, MAN.
YOU'RE NOT WORTH TALKING TO.
- ( stammers )
- YOU BASTARD!
DO YOU HAVE ANY IDEA
WHAT YOU'RE DOING?
- NOPE.
- I'LL MAKE YOU VERY SORRY
FOR THIS.
LOUSY PUNKS.
- OOH, I'M SCARED.
- ( laughs )
- Man: YOU.
YOUR IKUSEI'S BOY, AREN'T YOU?
DOING QUITE WELL
FOR YOURSELF, EH?
- I THOUGHT YOU DIED
IN A DITCH SOMEWHERE.
- DID YOU JOIN THE ORGANO
OR SOMETHING?
YOU GAVE IN TO THE POWERFUL.
IS THAT IT?
- THINK YOU COULD FOLLOW
IN YOUR OLD MAN'S FOOTSTEPS.
- I WILL NEVER ALLOW IT,
SOME YOUNG PUNK LIKE YOU,
I WON'T ALLOW TO EXIST.
THERE'S NO WAY IN HELL
THAT IKUSEI'S SON GETS
TO LIVE A BETTER LIFE THAN ME.
- I WON'T ALLOW PEOPLE
LIKE YOU TO EXIST, EITHER.
THERE'S NOTHING YOU CAN DO NOW.
NOTHING YOU CAN DO AT ALL.
- ( grunting )
- EXCEPT DRAG DOWN THOSE
WHO TRY TO RISE ABOVE.
SCUM.
LET GO.  LET ME GO.
BASTARD!
I'M SORRY.
I WAS COMPLETELY OUT OF LINE.
IT'S JUST THAT I'VE HAD
AN INFURIATING MOMENT.
LET'S GO.
I KNOW NOW WHERE THE MAN IS.
I WANTED TO GET OUT
OF THIS PLACE.
I SIMPLY COULDN'T STAND IT.
I HATE PEOPLE WHO ENVY OTHERS
AND DON'T DO ANYTHING
THEMSELVES.
AND I RESENTED THE FACT THAT
I WAS MY FATHER'S SON.
THAT'S WHY I CHANGED MY NAME.
AND THAT'S WHY I DID THIS.
THEY SAY THAT ACTS
SUCH AS SELF-INJURY
AND MUTILATION
LIKE GETTING TATTOOS
SIGNIFY AN ATTEMPT
TO DENY ONE'S BLOOD TIES.
I COULDN'T HAVE BEEN HAPPIER
TO GET TEXHNOLYZED.
I WANTED PROOF THAT I WAS
NOTHING LIKE THAT MAN.
- IF YOU HATE YOUR FATHER
SO MUCH, THEN WHY?
- I HAVE IT ON GOOD AUTHORITY
THE BOSS HERE
IS QUITE AN UNREASONABLE MAN.
YOU CAN RUN A BIT WILD
IF YOU'D LIKE.
WELL, SHALL WE GO?
- NICE WORK.
GET SOME REST.
- Toyama: IT'S BECAUSE
I'M GRATEFUL TO KOHAKURA.
THAT'S THE ANSWER
TO THE QUESTION YOU ASKED,
BECAUSE HE'S THE ONE
WHO FOUND ME AND RESCUED ME
FROM THAT PLACE.
WHAT I DID TODAY IS NOTHING.
IF I CAN REPAY HIM
BY DOING SO,
BUT SOMETIMES I CAN'T HELP
BUT WONDER IF THE DECISIONS
I'VE MADE ARE RIGHT.
I FEEL THAT WAY
ESPECIALLY AFTER WATCHING YOU.
I WONDER WHAT WILL
EVENTUALLY BECOME OF YOU.
I WONDER IF YOU CAN STILL REMAIN
EXACTLY WHO YOU ARE NOW.
SO WHAT DO YOU THINK
ABOUT YOURSELF?
WHAT IS IT YOU WANT TO DO?
- I JUST--
- GOOD NIGHT THEN.
- IN SHORT, WE SIMPLY HAVE TO
GET RID OF ONISHI.
ISN'T THAT SO, GREAT FATHER?
WE DON'T KNOW HOW THE CLASS
IS GOING TO REACT,
NOR THE UNION, NOR RACAN.
BESIDES, THE GENERAL PUBLIC
IS FEELING APPREHENSIVE.
WE MUST REPLACE
THE LEADER IMMEDIATELY.
AND BY DOING SO,
SHOW TO THE WORLD
THAT THE ORGANO HAS CHANGED.
- I AGREE AS WELL.
- BECAUSE I'M RIGHT.
- I SUGGEST WE CUT OUT
THE CANCER
WITHIN THE ORGANIZATION.
- THAT'S EXACTLY IT.
SO, GREAT FATHER--
- AND TO HELP GET THAT STARTED,
I HAD A COUPLE OF MY MEN
CAPTURE THE OBELISK BOMBER.
- ( gasps )
- HOWEVER, THIS BOMBER CLAIMS
THAT SOMEONE IN THIS ROOM
PUT HIM UP TO DOING IT.
- DO YOU HAVE THE MAN HERE?
- YES.
- BRING HIM IN.
- OH.
- ARE YOU THE ONE
WHO BOMBED THE OBELISK?
- ( gasping )
- WHO PUT YOU UP TO IT?
POINT TO HIM.
- TO KEIGO ONISHI
AND HIS RETURN TO POWER.
CHEERS.
YOU DON'T LOOK VERY HAPPY.
- I CAN'T SMILE FOR A DOCTOR
WHO'S SO INCONSIDERATE
THAT SHE GULPS DOWN ALCOHOL
IN FRONT OF HER PATIENT.
- OOPS.  SORRY.
- ( door opens )
- IS THERE SOMETHING WRONG?
- A MESSAGE FROM KOHAKURA.
HE SAYS HE'S GIVING ME
TO YOU AS A GIFT.
- AND THAT'S COMPLETELY FINE
WITH YOU?
- IF NOT, I WOULDN'T HAVE COME.
TO TELL THE TRUTH,
I REALLY DON'T KNOW
WHAT IS IT THAT I WANT TO DO
OR WHAT IT IS
THAT I SHOULD DO.
BUT I'M NOT GOING BACK
TO WHERE I WAS BEFORE.
AND I HAVE NO PLACE
TO GO NOW.
I KNOW THAT MUCH.
- Onishi:
THEN DO AS YOU WISH.
- QUITE STRANGE THAT BOY.
- ( panting )
YOU KNOW I'M RIGHT.
YOU SAW IT, DIDN'T YOU?
- WHAT DO YOU WANNA
KNOW THAT FOR?
- I DON'T REALLY KNOW.
- I CAN SEE EVERYTHING NOW.
BUT I DON'T WANT TO.
I DON'T WANT TO SEE
ANYTHING ANYMORE.
- ( theme music playing )
- ( singing in Japanese )