- Man: IF THERE'S
ANYTHING YOU WANT,
ANYTHING AT ALL,
COME TO ME.
I'M YOUR GUARDIAN ANGEL.
- ( theme music playing )
- WHERE ARE WE GOING?
THIS ISN'T THE RIGHT WAY.
- THERE IS A BOY WHO LONGS
FOR THE WORLD ON THE HILL.
AND I WANT TO SHOW IT TO HIM.
I WANT TO LET HIM KNOW
WHAT THE TRUTH IS.
- WHAT GOOD IS THAT
GOING TO DO?
WHY DO YOU WANT
TO HURRY THIS?
- I'M NOT IN A HURRY AT ALL.
THIS CITY IS PICKING UP SPEED
ON ITS OWN.
THOUGH YOU PROBABLY
CAN'T KEEP UP.
I WANNA LET THE YOUNG PEOPLE
KNOW EXACTLY WHAT I'M THINKING.
JUST LIKE THIS ONE AND THE ONE
WE'RE GOING TO VISIT NOW.
- ( panting )
- ( screaming )
- ( gunshot )
- ( grunts )
- WHO THE HELL ARE YOU?
- ( explosion )
- WE'RE NOT OPEN JUST YET.
- HEY, IF YOU SEE ONISHI,
YOU TELL US RIGHT AWAY.
GOT THAT?
- ( men running )
- HMM.  THE LEAST YOU COULD
HAVE DONE IS SHUT THE DOOR.
I'M SORRY,
BUT THAT'S ALL I COULD GET
IN THE LITTLE TIME I HAD.
- IT'S NOT MUCH.
- DON'T ACT LIKE A STRANGER.
I HAVE NO USE FOR IT.
IT'S JUST LIKE TEN YEARS AGO.
- HE'S NOT AT THE WOMAN'S PLACE,
EITHER.
- WELL, I GUESS THERE'S NO RUSH
TO TAKE CARE OF IT.
- MR. TSUJINAKA AND MR. IZAKI
HAVE BOTH SENT US A MESSAGE.
THEY'D LIKE TO CONTRIBUTE
A FEW OF THEIR MEN
DURING THIS TIME OF CRISIS.
- TSUJINAKA AND IZAKI?
THOSE OLD FARTS.
THEY CAN SEE I MEAN BUSINESS.
AND NOW THEY'RE EAGER
TO COME ALONG FOR THE RIDE.
- SONODA AND KOHAKURA?
- NOTHING.
- WELL, IT WOULDN'T DO ANY GOOD
TO CREATE A FACTION
WITH A BUNCH OF HALFWITS,
ESPECIALLY IF THOSE TWO
GET IN LEAGUE WITH EACH OTHER.
OH, WHAT THE HELL?
SINCE WE'VE GOT ENOUGH MANPOWER,
GO SNATCH A SLICE
OF THE RACAN'S TERRITORY.
- RIGHT.
- YOU KNOW WHAT TO DO.
- WE'LL DEPLOY MEN FROM
THE TSUJINAKA AND IZAKI OFFICES
TO THE FRONTLINE.
- I WASN'T EXPECTING YOU.
- I HEARD THAT YOU WERE HERE,
MR. SONODA.
IT'S THE HEIGHT OF FOLLY
FOR THEM TO IGNORE YOU.
YOUR OFFICE HAS THE GREATEST
STRENGTH AMONG US.
- I HEAR MIZUNO'S ACTING
LIKE HE'S IN CHARGE.
HOWEVER, IF IT'S BETWEEN
MIZUNO AND KEIGO--
- I WAS UNDER THE IMPRESSION
YOU REALLY DIDN'T LIKE KEIGO.
- AND WHAT'S YOUR OPINION
ON THIS, MR. KOHAKURA?
- IF YOU DON'T DO ANYTHING
TO RESOLVE THE SITUATION,
MIZUNO WILL TAKE
ALL THE CREDIT.
- I'M GOING TO FOLLOW
YOUR EXAMPLE--
AVOID POINTLESS CONFLICTS AND
WAIT IT OUT UNTIL EVERYONE ELSE
IS EXHAUSTED.
- HMM.
- ( door opens )
- HMM?
- SHINJI, SOME OF THE ORGANO
HAVE MOVED IN
AND STARTED PROWLING AROUND
IN OUR TERRITORY.
- SHINJI.
- ALL WHILE WE
IN THE SALVATION UNION
WERE BUSY KILLING EACH OTHER.
NOW IT MAKES SENSE.
MAYBE THAT'S THE REASON
WHY ONISHI SHOWED UP ALONE.
- WHAT'S STRANGE IS THEY'RE
LOOKING FOR ONISHI AS WELL.
- FOR HIM, TOO?
HOW MANY OF US
DO WE HAVE READY TO GO?
- I'D SAY ABOUT 60%, BUT SOME
OF THE OTHERS ARE STILL HURT.
- PERHAPS IT'S
MORE LIKE SOME
OF THE OTHERS
RAN OUT ON YOU.
- HMM?
JUST LIKE YOU.
- YOU TOLD ME THAT THE RACAN
WAS MADE UP OF VOLUNTEERS.
THEN THEY'RE ALSO FREE
TO BAIL OUT.  AM I RIGHT?
IN A TIME OF ABSOLUTE CHAOS,
A SYSTEMATICALLY GOVERNED GROUP
IS STRONGER THAN ONE THAT'S NOT.
IF YOU WENT HEAD TO HEAD
WITH THE ORGANO,
THE RESULTS WOULD BE
PRETTY OBVIOUS.
- YOU DON'T KNOW NOTHING
ABOUT THIS,
SO SHUT THE HELL UP.
- THEN I GUESS YOU MUST HAVE
A BETTER IDEA
OF HOW
WE SHOULD HANDLE THIS.
- MATTER OF FACT, I DO.
THERE'S SOMEONE.  SOMEONE
FROM THE TOP OF THE HILL
THAT'S VISITING THE CITY NOW.
- YOU DON'T MEAN--
- SO WHAT DO YOU THINK OF THAT?
- A CHANCE.
MAYBE A SMALL ONE.
NOW THAT THE DIG SITE
HAS BEEN VANDALIZED,
THEIR TRUST IN THE ORGANO
HAS BEEN SOMEWHAT SHAKEN.
SO THERE'S ROOM FOR US
TO CAPITALIZE ON THAT.
- TO WIN A THREE-SIDED WAR,
YOU CAN'T SEE THINGS
THE SAME WAY
AS YOUR OPPONENTS.
AS IT HAPPENS, WE'RE ON
OUR WAY TO GO TAKE A LOOK.
WANNA JOIN US?
- SHINJI, DON'T LISTEN
TO ANY OF THIS GUY'S CRAP.
- UNTIL I GET BACK,
DON'T MAKE ANY MOVES
WITHOUT MY OKAY.
YOU GOT THAT, HAL?
- SPLIT UP INTO GROUPS AND GO
PATROL AROUND THE BORDERS.
- BUT SHINJI SAID NOT TO.
- SHINJI JUST SAID NOT
TO ATTACK.
WHO THE HELL WOULDN'T BE
ON THE ALERT
WHEN THE ENEMY HAS STARTED
CAMPING OUT IN HIS FRONT YARD,
YOU FRIGGIN' MORON?!
- ( engines revving )
- LOOK, IT'S ONISHI.
- TERU.
- ( grunting )
- ( shouts )
- THERE WAS A STRANGER
WHO RECENTLY VISITED
YOUR HANGOUT.
- ( gagging )
- WHERE IS HE?
I DON'T KNOW!
- ( flesh rips )
- ( choking )
( screams )
- TALK.
SO YOU DIDN'T RUN AWAY.
LET'S GET GOING.
- ( coughing )
- ARE YOU ALL RIGHT,
GREAT FATHER?
- WHAT'S TAKING SO LONG?
- APPARENTLY, THE ODOR IS
DISTURBING TO THE DELEGATES,
SO THE CHAMBER IS BEING
RECLEANED.
- I SEE.
- GREAT FATHER, HOW ARE
YOU GOING TO EXPLAIN
ABOUT KEIGO
TO THE DELEGATE?
- I AGREE THE
WAY KEIGO DEALT
WITH NAKAHARA'S YOUNG MEN
WAS HARSH.
HOWEVER, IT MAY AS WELL BE PROOF
THAT HE IS TRULY CONCERNED
ABOUT THE ORGANIZATION'S FUTURE.
- SIR.
- HUH.
WHEN THE LIKES OF MIZUNO
ARE ABLE TO TAKE CONTROL,
THAT'S THE END OF THE ORGANO.
DO YOU KNOW HOW OFTEN
HE VISITED ME IN THE HOSPITAL?
- I DON'T KNOW.
- NOT EVEN ONCE.
BUT KEIGO COMES EVERY WEEK.
WHEN YOU'RE OLDER, YOU NOTICE
SUCH THINGS WITHOUT EVEN TRYING.
SABU, THAT'S THE KIND OF THING
THAT ULTIMATELY MATTERS
IN A MAN.
- SO THAT'S ONE OF THE CLASS.
- YES, THOSE ARE THE PEOPLE
OF THE CELESTIAL WORLD
THAT YOU HAVE BEEN LONGING FOR.
BUT IN TRUTH,
THEY ARE NOTHING
BUT WEAK INVALIDS.
- HUH?
WHAT ARE YOU TRYING TO DO?
- THE ORGANO IS YOUR MOST
HATED ENEMY, RIGHT?
- ( grunting )
- ( gasps, grunts )
- WHAT THE HELL DID
YOU DO THAT FOR?
- JUST KEEP YOUR MOUTH SHUT
AND WATCH.
I'LL DESTROY WHAT'S KEEPING
YOUR POWER BOTTLED UP FOR YOU.
- ( gun cocks )
- YOU'RE ACTING SILLY.
HAVEN'T YOU FIGURED OUT
THAT I'M YOUR FRIEND?
- NOW I GET IT.
YOU'RE THE ONE HOPPING AROUND
AND SETTING THINGS UP.
IT'S TOO MUCH OF A COINCIDENCE
THE WAY YOU SHOW UP
ONLY WHEN IT SUITS YOU.
LIKE TODAY.
THEN IT YOU WHO BLEW UP
OUR DEN, WASN'T IT?
- I GUESS YOU'RE EVEN SMARTER
THAN I FIRST THOUGHT.
- ANSWER ME.
- WHAT IF I DID?
- WHO THE HELL ARE YOU?
- TO GIVE AN ANSWER SIMPLE
ENOUGH THAT EVEN YOU
CAN UNDERSTAND,
I CAN ONLY SAY THAT I CAME
FROM A COMPLETELY
DIFFERENT WORLD.
IF THAT MAN DIES HERE,
IT WILL LEAD
TO VERY EXCITING THINGS,
DON'T YOU THINK?
THAT'S WHEN YOU COME
INTO THE PICTURE.
- YOU'RE JUST HAVING FUN
MESSING THINGS UP.
BUT IN THE END,
THAT'S ALL YOU'RE DOING.
- AND YOU'RE DOING
THE EXACT SAME THING.
ALTHOUGH YOU DON'T SEEM TO KNOW
WHAT TRULY LIES BEYOND.
BUT I HAD REALLY HOPED
THAT YOU WOULD UNDERSTAND.
- IF IT WAS ME,
I'D DO BETTER.
I WON'T LET YOU KILL THAT MAN.
- ( gun cocks )
- THIS SPECTACLE IS ONE BIG
EVENT THAT I'M ORGANIZING.
I'M DOING THIS IN ORDER
TO CREATE A LEADER
WHO WILL AWAKEN YOU ALL.
AND I'M THINKING
ABOUT GIVING YOU A CHANCE
TO BE THE FIRST ONE
TO STEP FORWARD
AND TAKE THAT POSITION.
SO BELIEVE ME WHEN I SAY
THAT NO ONE IN THIS CITY
IS TRULY AWAKE.
- Man: IS IT BEYOND THE ORGANO'S
ABILITY TO GOVERN THIS PLACE?
- Man #2: NO, ABSOLUTELY
BY NO MEANS IS IT.
- Man #3: ONCE RAFFIA IS LOST,
THIS CITY IS WORTHLESS.
YOU WILL BE WORTHLESS AS WELL.
- THE DAMAGE TO THE DIG SITE
IS VERY MINOR.
AND THE RECOVERY IS JUST
A MATTER OF TIME.
- Ishii: ONISHI.
- GET DOWN!
- ( gasps )
- DAMN.
- ( gun cocks )
- ( gunshot )
- ( grunts )
- NOW THAT'S MORE LIKE IT.
- NO, DON'T GO.
IF YOU GO.
- MR. ONISHI.
YOU'RE DETERMINED TO GET
IN MY WAY
EVERY TIME, AREN'T YOU?
I HEARD YOU CAN HEAR THE VOICE
OF THE CITY.
SO TELL ME,
WHAT'S IT SAYING
ABOUT ME?
OH, BY THE WAY,
YOUR WIFE WAS PITIFUL.
DIED SO EASILY OR MAYBE IT
WAS ALL THE BETTER FOR HER.
AFTER ALL, SHE WAS
HALF-DEAD ALREADY.
ALL BECAUSE OF YOU, MR. ONISHI.
- ( gasps )
- ( coughing )
( gasping )
- MR. ONISHI,
IT WOULD BE NICE IF YOU'D CRY
AND SCREAM AT LEAST A LITTLE
SINCE I CAN'T ENJOY THINGS
LIKE THIS ABOVE GROUND.
- YOU--
WHAT ARE YOU TRYING TO DO?
- ESSENTIALLY THE SAME AS YOU,
MR. ONISHI.
ALTHOUGH MY METHODS
ARE FAR MORE ADVANCED
THAN YOURS APPEAR TO BE
BECAUSE I CAME FROM THE OUTSIDE,
I CAN SEE A LOT OF THINGS.
MR. ONISHI,
AS BLIND AS YOU ARE,
IT'S NO FUN BEING ALIVE,
IS IT?
SO WHY DON'T YOU JUST GO
AND JOIN YOUR WIFE?
- Toyama: HEY.
- Yoshii: GET LOST.
- ( grunts )
- ( screaming )
- ( panting )
- ( groaning )
- Ran:
AFTER ALL...
NOTHING EVER CHANGES.
- Yoshii: SAKIMURA.
- YOSHII...
YOU MUST BE EXHAUSTED.
- ( gunshot )
- ( theme music playing )
- ( singing in Japanese )