- Man: IF THERE'S
ANYTHING YOU WANT,
ANYTHING AT ALL,
COME TO ME.
I'M YOUR GUARDIAN ANGEL.
- ( theme music playing )
- Ran: IN THE END,
YOU WILL DESTROY EVERYTHING.
YOU WILL HURT MANY PEOPLE.
YOU WILL BE ALL ALONE
IN THE END.
- Onishi: I NEVER WOULD HAVE
THOUGHT THAT HE PERSONALLY
KNEW THE SEER.
PERHAPS, THE EXPERIENCE
WILL BE GOOD FOR HIM.
AFTER ALL, RUSHING OFF
TOWARDS ONE'S DOOM
IS THE EASIEST THING
TO DO.
- HE DOESN'T APPEAR TO HAVE
CHANGED TO ME.
- NOBODY GOES UNSCATHED
WHEN THEY'RE TOLD THEIR FUTURE.
I NEED A LITTLE REST.
- Doc: I'VE BEEN SENDING YOU
REPORTS AS WE AGREED.
NOW HOW ABOUT YOU KEEPING
YOUR WORD IN RETURN.
I WON'T DO ANYTHING
LIKE THIS!
- GIMME A GOOD ONE.
I'VE BEEN WORKING
TOO HARD THESE DAYS.
AND IT'S BEEN TAKING
A REAL TOLL ON MY BODY.
- ( gasps )
- ( gunshot )
- Doc: WHAT DO YOU DO
WITH THIS JUNK?
- Man: WELL, I DON'T KNOW.
BUT THERE ARE BUYERS.
- WHO?
THE CLASS?
WHY DO THEY NEED THIS JUNK?
SOMEBODY TOLD ME THAT YOU MIGHT
HAVE SOME RAFFIA HERE.
- WHAT THE HELL IS THAT,
HUH?
- HOW MUCH?
- ( laughs )
- ( gasps )
- I REALLY DON'T HAVE ANY.
THE RAFFIA SUPPLY IS REALLY
SCARCE THESE DAYS.
SOME OF THE DIGGERS USED
TO BRING SOME TO ME,
BUT NONE OF 'EM COME
THESE DAYS.
- ( whimpers )
LET GO OF ME.
- COME AGAIN. ( laughs )
- Woman: IT DOESN'T LOOK VERY
COMFORTABLE, DOES IT?
- Onishi:
DON'T RETURN SOMEONE'S FAVOR
BY COMPLAINING ABOUT IT.
- I'M SORRY.
- EXECUTIVES FROM TWO OFFICES
WERE ATTACKED.
AND SONODA'S OFFICE RECEIVED
A RETALIATION IN THE SAME NIGHT.
IT DOESN'T MAKE SENSE.
IGNORING TSUJINAKA AND IZAKI,
SONODA HAS ALWAYS MADE SURE
TO KEEP THE YOUNGER MEMBERS
OF HIS OFFICE IN LINE.
THERE'S NOTHING GAINED
BY SETTING HIM UP.
- THOSE THREE OFFICES
ARE MAKING INQUIRIES
THROUGH THEIR LOWER LEVEL
MEMBERS TO LEARN THE TRUTH
ABOUT THIS MATTER.
- THEY CANNOT SEE
THE REAL ENEMY.
- BUT HE DOES EXIST.
WE ALMOST GOT KILLED IN GABE.
- SO YOU FINALLY DECIDED
TO OPEN THAT MOUTH OF YOURS.
AT LEAST YOU SEEM TO BE
ON THE RIGHT TRACK.
- ( telephone rings )
- ( picks up telephone )
WHAT IS IT NOW?
LET ME SEE YOUR HAND.
NOT THAT ONE.
MOVE IT.
RIGHT.
I'LL SEND HIM OVER.
GOODBYE.
- ( clicks )
- GO AND HAVE DOC
TAKE A LOOK AT IT.
AND CHECK ON HER AS WELL.
YOUR MIND IS WORKING SOMEWHAT
QUICKER NOW, ISN'T IT?
IF THEY'RE SEEKING TO TAKE OUR
LIVES, THEN IT'LL COME
AS NO SURPRISE THE DOCTOR
MAY BE BE IN DANGER AS WELL.
BUT BE CAREFUL.  THAT DOCTOR
IS QUITE AN INTUITIVE WOMAN.
- YOU'RE LOOKING VERY SHARP.
FIRST ONISHI AND NOW YOU.
I FEEL GOOD WHEN THE MEN I TAKE
A SPECIAL INTEREST IN
GET AHEAD IN THE WORLD.
- WHAT ARE YOU DOING?
- I JUST FEEL LIKE CELEBRATING.
LET'S HAVE A TOAST.
YOU START FROM THE OUTSIDE.
YOU STILL LACK CULTURAL
SOPHISTICATION.
- ( silverware clatters )
- ( laughs )
I'M VERY SORRY.  YOU CAME HERE
TO HAVE YOU HAND FIXED.
THEY'VE COMPLETELY BECOME PART
OF YOUR BODY.
DO YOU REMEMBER?
IN THE BEGINNING,
YOU SAID YOU DIDN'T WANT THEM.
AFTER ALL THIS TIME,
DO YOU STILL THINK THAT WAY?
THAT ARM AND LEG HAVE SHOWN
YOU MANY THINGS, HAVEN'T THEY?
- JUST SOME LEFT OVER MEMORIES
FROM MY PARENTS.
- DO YOU WANT TO SEE
MANY MORE THINGS?
- ( beeps )
- ( grunts )
- THAT'S NOTHING WE SHOULD MAKE
A BIG DEAL OUT OF.
IT'S JUST THOSE WHO
DON'T WANNA STEP OFF THE STAGE
AND LOSE THE ATTENTION
THEY'VE GAINED.
IT'S ONLY NATURAL.
THERE'S NOTHING NEW ABOUT IT.
- YOU SOUND UNCONCERNED.
YET, YOU OR I COULD BE NEXT.
- WHAT ARE YOU
SO WORRIED ABOUT?
THEN AGAIN,
IF I WERE IN YOUR SHOES,
I'D PROBABLY BE FEELING
THE SAME WAY AS YOU ARE.
JUST BE PATIENT.
THE CHANCE WILL PRESENT ITSELF.
YOU'LL GET YOUR RIGHTFUL
POSITION BACK SOONER OR LATER.
IN THE MEANTIME,
LET'S JUST SIT BACK
AND WATCH THEM
DESTROY THEMSELVES.
- ( beeping )
- THIS IS A NEW EXPERIENCE.
YOU ARE NOW THE MOST EVOLVED
PERSON IN THIS CITY.
WHEN THEY SEE YOU, EVERYTHING
I'VE BEEN STRIVING FOR
WILL BECOME CLEAR TO THEM,
ESPECIALLY HOW THEY SHOULD
UTILIZE THEIR OWN TECHNOLOGY.
YOU'RE QUITE ADORABLE,
DEAR BOY.
TIME TO GO NOW.
YOU'RE FREE.
NOW BE A GOOD BOY
AND LIE STILL.
- ( door closes )
- ( engine turns over )
- ALL RIGHT THEN, LET'S GO.
- WHERE AM I GOING?
- JUST DO AS YOU'RE TOLD.
THAT'S ALL.
- YES, SIR.
- WHERE ARE YOU GOING?
WHERE?
- I'M GOING HOME.
- HOME?
- MY REAL HOME.
I NO LONGER NEED TO STAY
IN THIS CITY.
- WHAT ABOUT US?  WHAT NOW?
- US?
YOU MEAN ONISHI AND YOURSELF.
EVEN IF I'M GONE, YOU CAN AT
LEAST GET YOUR TEXHNOLYZED LIMBS
REPAIRED IN THE CITY.
YOU'RE WORRIED ABOUT SOMEONE
BESIDES YOURSELF.
HOW CAN THAT BE WHEN YOU
WON'T EVEN FALL FOR ME?
SO IS ONISHI THAT FASCINATING?
NOW I'M MAD.
BUT YOU, DEAR BOY,
SHOULDN'T WORRY ABOUT ANYTHING.
THAT'S BECAUSE YOU'RE
COMING WITH ME.
AS A REWARD,
I'M GOING TO GIVE YOU
CULTURAL SOPHISTICATION.
A MAN'S CHARM IS ESSENTIALLY
SOPHISTICATION.
AND AS A RESULT, HIS IDEALS
ARE LED BY IT.
I'LL TURN YOU INTO MUCH MORE
OF A MAN THAN ONISHI EVER WAS.
I'LL TEACH YOU THAT
TEXHNOLYZATION DOES NOT EXIST
FOR THE PURPOSE OF VIOLENCE.
- TAKE ME BACK RIGHT NOW.
- YOU DON'T HAVE ANY
UNDERSTANDING, DO YOU?
EVERYTHING IS AT MY WILL,
INCLUDING YOU
AND HOW THE PEOPLE
OF THIS CITY WILL EVOLVE.
- DETACH IT AND CONNECT IT
TO THE OTHER ONE.
- HEY.  HEY!
- YES.
- WHERE'S THE REST?
- I ALREADY TOLD YOU THAT WE
CAN'T BRING THEM ALL AT ONCE.
- THEY SAY THE SOONER
YOU DELIVER,
THE MORE YOU GET PAID.
- THEY SAY?
SERIOUSLY.  ARE YOU GONNA
START A WAR OR SOMETHING?
- JUST MIND YOUR OWN BUSINESS.
WE'LL BE BACK IN FIVE DAYS.
- OPEN IT.
I KNOW YOU CAN SEE ME.
OPEN IT.
I ALREADY KNOW.
YOU'RE COLLECTING RESOURCES
FOR TEXHNOLYZATION.
YOU'VE READ THE REPORTS
I SENT YOU, DIDN'T YOU?
YOU NEED MY EXPERTISE.
IT'S RIGHT HERE.
AND LOOK, I BROUGHT THE RESULTS
OF MY RESEARCH.
HE'S THE MOST EVOLVED HUMAN
IN THIS CITY.
IT'S ABOUT TIME THAT YOU
ACKNOWLEDGED MY ACCOMPLISHMENTS.
WITH MY TECHNIQUES,
TEXHNOLYZATION AND HUMANKIND
CAN BE MERGED EVEN FURTHER.
IN JUST A FEW GENERATIONS,
THEY WOULD BE PERFECT
HUMAN BEINGS.
AS LONG AS I'M HERE,
SOMEDAY THE PEOPLE OUTSIDE--
- ( clicks )
- ( pants )
- HURRY UP AND OPEN IT.
WHAT ARE YOU WAITING FOR?
I DEMAND THAT YOU LET ME IN.
- ( thuds )
- ( explosion )
- ( gasping )
WAIT!
WHY?  WHY ARE YOU DOING THIS?
- ( gasps )
- ( explosion )
- LET GO OF ME.
I'M GOING BACK IN THERE.
WHY?
WHAT DID I DO?
WHY DON'T THEY NEED ME?
- YOUR HOME, IT'S IN THERE,
ISN'T IT?
- YES.
- WHAT'S IT LIKE THERE?
IT'S JUST A CITY.
BUT THE PEOPLE WHO LIVE THERE,
YOU COULDN'T POSSIBLY
BEGIN TO UNDERSTAND.
- IF I CAN'T KNOW,
IF I DON'T KNOW ANYTHING,
IS THAT WHY I'M GOING TO
BE LEFT ALL ALONE?
- WHAT?
- SINCE I DON'T KNOW ANYTHING,
WILL I DESTROY EVERYTHING?
- WHAT ARE YOU TALKING ABOUT?
- THEN TEACH ME SOMEDAY.
TEACH ME THE THINGS
THAT YOU KNOW ABOUT.
( grunts )
- ( grunting )
- ( laughs )
- ( gunshots )
- Doc:
HOW CAN IT BE?
ALL OF IT...
GONE.
- NOT YET.
NOT ALL OF IT'S GONE YET.
- THAT'S NOT TRUE.
SOONER OR LATER,
EVERYTHING WILL BE GONE.
- ( theme music playing )
- ( singing in Japanese )