- Man: IF THERE'S
ANYTHING YOU WANT,
ANYTHING AT ALL,
COME TO ME.
I'M YOUR GUARDIAN ANGEL.
- ( theme music playing )
- ( growls )
HUH?
- ( screams )
- SHINJI!
- ONISHI.
- ONISHI!
- STOP IT.
- ( sighs )
- ( whistles )
- HUH?
- ( gasping )
- ( shouts )
- WHOM TO KEEP ALIVE?
- TURN RIGHT QUICKLY.
- ( tires screeching )
- ( gunshot )
- RATS!
DON'T SLOW DOWN.
- HMM.
- Onishi: AS IF HE HASN'T GOT
A CARE IN THE WORLD.
- Mana:
WHERE SHOULD WE GO?
- LET HIM SLEEP
IN YOUR APARTMENT.
- YES.
- ( beeping )
- Man: REALLY?  ONISHI?
THEY DID, HUH?  I SEE.
- WELL, YEAH.
EVERYTHING'S GOING TO PLAN.
- ( coin rattles )
- ( grunts )
- HMM?
DID YOU JUST HEAR
SOMETHING?
- ( gasps ) NO, I DIDN'T.
- ( telephone rings )
- THE OBELISK?  HOW ABOUT
THE SUBTERRANEAN DIG SITE?
- SO THEN IT'S TRUE.
- YES, I SEE.
YOU MEAN IT CAN BE RESTORED
IN NO TIME?
GIVE IT TOP PRIORITY.
- Man:
SO WE'VE GOT A PROBLEM.
- NOW IT'S GETTING INTERESTING.
- Man:
WE LEAVE ONISHI IN CHARGE
AND LOOK WHAT HAPPENS.
- THE PROBLEM IS
HOW ARE WE GOING TO WEATHER
THE COMING STORM?
- IF THEY'RE COMING TO SEE US,
THE ONLY WAY TO HANDLE THIS
DELICATE SITUATION IS TO HAVE
MR. GOTO MEET WITH HIM.
- MR. SONODA,
MR. TSUJINAKA,
YOU DON'T MEAN TO HAVE
GOTO THE GREAT FATHER,
GO TO THEM EMPTY-HANDED,
DO YOU?
I MEAN, THINK ABOUT HIS AGE.
WE'RE TALKING ABOUT DRAGGING
OUT A HOSPITALIZED MAN.
WE CAN'T JUST ALLOW HIM
TO BE HUMILIATED LIKE THAT.
- AND YOUR POINT?
- WITHOUT PUNISHING
THE MAN RESPONSIBLE,
HOW CAN WE
MAINTAIN DISCIPLINE?
IT'S ALL BECAUSE OF ONISHI.
HE SAT ON THE FENCE AND STRUCK
A DEAL WITH THE ENEMY.
- SO, GENTLEMEN,
DOES ANYONE HERE DISAGREE?
- NOW I BROUGHT THIS UP,
SO OF COURSE,
I'LL CARRY IT OUT.
JUST TRUST ME.
- HOW DID IT GO, SIR?
- THINGS JUST GOT A LOT
MORE COMPLICATED.
I HAVE A LITTLE JOB FOR YOU.
- SO NOW?
- I'M RETURNING TO THE OFFICE.
CALL ME WHEN HE WAKES UP.
- YES, SIR, I WILL.
- ( explosion )
- OH!
- THIS WAY!
- ( glass shatters )
- ( shouting )
- ( gunshots )
- ( laughing )
- LOOKS LIKE ONISHI WASN'T
IN HIS OFFICE AFTER ALL.
- ( laughs )
HEY, GO GET ME SOME KOI.
GO ON.
- ( panting )
- ( engine revving )
- TOYAMA.
- MR. ONISHI.
YOU SHOULDN'T GO BACK
TO YOUR OFFICE RIGHT NOW.
THAT IS NO LONGER
A SAFE PLACE FOR YOU TO BE.
I HIGHLY SUGGEST THAT YOU'D
BETTER KEEP MOVING.
- WHAT DO YOU MEAN?
- THE DIG SITE
HAS BEEN VANDALIZED.
- WHO'S RESPONSIBLE FOR THIS?
- THE PEOPLE UP ON THE HILL
ARE COMING DOWN.
THE EXECUTIVE BOARD
HAS DECIDED THAT YOU
SHALL TAKE RESPONSIBILITY.
- ( gasps )
- THE MEN FROM MIZUNO'S OFFICE
ARE NOW OUT LOOKING FOR YOU.
- MIZUNO?
- WE SUGGEST THAT YOU MAKE HASTE
TO GET OUT OF HERE.
- WHY?
WHY ARE YOU
TELLING ME THIS?
IS THIS KOHAKURA'S IDEA?
- MR. ONISHI, IF YOU THINK
SOMEONE'S PULLING THE STRINGS
BEHIND ALL THESE DISTURBANCES,
THEN PERHAPS
I COULD INVESTIGATE FOR YOU.
- ( man humming )
- ( door opens )
- HMM?
- I NEED TO USE THIS.
- MR. ONISHI!
- ( telephone rings )
- ( clicks )
- MANA, I NEED YOU TO GET OUT
OF THERE IMMEDIATELY.
MANA.
HEY!  WHAT'S WRONG?
MANA!
WHO'S THERE?
- MR. ONISHI, I WENT THROUGH
SO MUCH TROUBLE
TO ARRANGE THINGS, BUT YOU
JUST HAD TO PUT THINGS BACK.
YOU KNOW, YOU'RE JUST
WAY TOO PETTY-MINDED.
OH, MR. ONISHI.
I THINK I'M GONNA HAVE YOU
JOIN THE SPECTACLE
WHETHER YOU LIKE IT OR NOT.
PERHAPS I SHOULD HAVE
YOUR WIFE JOIN AS WELL.
- WHAT DO YOU WANT?
- WHO ME?  LET ME SEE.
A SPECTACLE.
THAT'S WHAT I WANT.
A SPECTACLE
WITH THE ENTIRE CITY
INVOLVED.
- HELLO!  MANA!
- ( growls )
- ( gasps )
( grunts )
- FOUR OF THEM.
- HUH?
- ( coughing )
- WHAT IS THIS?
- ( gasps ) OW!
- LOOK, MY FRIEND.  I JUST
WANT YOU TO TELL ME SOMETHING.
PLEASE TELL ME
THE CURRENT STATUS
OF YOUR PEOPLE'S SPECTACLE.
I SAID PLEASE.
- ( telephone rings )
- Toyama: MR. ONISHI.
- TOYAMA.
- I'VE GOT SOMETHING.
HE WAS VISITING THE RACAN.
- THE RACAN?
- ARE YOU GOING?
- WELL, I SUPPOSE IT'S NONE
OF MY BUSINESS.
- TELL ME.
DAMN YOU!  WHY DON'T
YOU TELL ME SOMETHING?
- HMM?
- WHERE ARE YOU GOING,
SAKIMURA?
- YOSHII, LET'S STOP THIS.
YOU DON'T NEED MY HELP ANYMORE.
- OH.  NOW YOU'RE ACTING
LIKE A COWARD.
NO QUITTING HALF WAY.
HI.  VERY SOON THE PEOPLE
UP ON THE HILL
WILL BE COMING DOWN.
- PLEASE TELL ME
WHAT ARE YOU THINKING NOW?
- I THINK THIS WILL BE
A VERY NICE ATTRACTION
FOR THE SPECTACLE.
- BUT WHY?
THIS COULDN'T HAVE BEEN
AN ORDER.
- ORDER?  I DON'T CARE
ABOUT SUCH THINGS ANYMORE.
I WANT TO ENLIGHTEN
THE PEOPLE OF LUX
SO THEY CAN BELIEVE
IN THEIR OWN POWER.
NOW I'M BEGINNING TO SEE
THAT IS MY MISSION.
- YOSHII.
- SAKIMURA.
WHAT IS IT THAT YOU'VE DONE
SINCE YOU CAME TO THIS CITY?
YOU'VE USED IT AS A SHIELD
TO HIDE BEHIND.
THAT'S NOT RIGHT.
YOU HAVE TO TRY TO IMPROVE.
YOU HAVE TO GIVE MORE MEANING
TO YOUR MEANINGLESS LIFE.
- YOSHII.
- AND YOU'RE COMING
WITH US, TOO.
-  WHERE ARE WE GOING?
- MR. ONISHI WANTS TO SEE YOU.
- ( theme music playing )
- ( singing in Japanese )