- ( theme music plays )
- Man: IF THERE'S ANYTHING
YOU WANT, ANYTHING AT ALL,
COME TO ME.
I'LL BE YOUR GUARDIAN ANGEL.
- ( footsteps )
- ( banging )
- OPEN IT.
- ( lock turning )
- ( heavy breathing )
- LEAVE US, PLEASE.
- ( door opens and closes )
- ( trembling )
- AT LAST, IT SEEMS THAT YOU'VE
FINALLY BECOME MY TYPE.
- ( grunting )
- ( bang )
- Ichise:
WHAT DO YOU MEAN?
- Doc:
NOTHING.
- ( door opens )
- NOW, DOC--
- ARE YOU GOING
TO KILL HIM NOW?
RIGHT HERE, EVEN THOUGH
THIS BOY BELONGS TO ME?
- ( chuckles )
- Onishi: SO YOU GOT
THE ORGANO TO GO ALONG
WITH YOUR CAPRICIOUSNESS,
SATISFIED?
- AS A COMPANION FOR HIM,
THIS CITY IS MUCH MORE
SUITABLE THAN I AM.
- Onishi: THIS CITY DOESN'T
HAVE ANY TIME TO SPARE
FOR A DOG LIKE HIM.
- ( chuckles )
- NOW WHAT DO YOU FIND SO FUNNY?
- I'M JUST WONDERING
BY WHOSE WILL
HE'S STILL BEING KEPT ALIVE.
BY YOURS,
OR MINE?
OR PERHAPS THE CITY
OF LUX ITSELF.
- HM.
- ( squeaking )
- LOOKS LIKE I FOUND SOMEONE
ELSE TO KEEP ME COMPANY.
- HM.
- ( train bell )
- YOU LOOK WORN OUT.
- DO I?
I'VE ALWAYS LIKED RAILROADS.
I GUESS THAT MY DREAM FINALLY
CAME TRUE WHEN I ARRIVED HERE.
- LOOKING AT YOUR HANDS,
PEOPLE WOULD THINK
YOU'RE A DIFFERENT MAN.
- ACTUALLY, I AM
A DIFFERENT MAN.
- IN THE WORLD ABOVE, THE FACT
THAT YOU EVEN ONCE EXISTED
IS NOW BECOMING OBSCURE.
- SO IT'S THE SAME AS ALWAYS
UP THERE.
- NO CHANGES WHATSOEVER,
ANNOYINGLY SO.
- HUH.
- AS SOMEONE WHO ONCE ASPIRED
TO BECOME LIKE YOU,
I'D LIKE TO ASK YOU A QUESTION.
TATSUYA SAKIMURA
IS ALREADY DEAD.
THE MAN YOU'RE TALKING
TO RIGHT NOW IS SOMEONE ELSE.
- THEN HOW SHOULD I REPORT
THIS TO THE PEOPLE ABOVE?
- IS THERE ANYTHING
THAT'S BOTHERING YOU?
- NO.
- Man:
MAN, HE'S SUCH AN ASSHOLE.
( laughing )
- Shinji: YO.
THERE'S A MODEL
YOU DON'T SEE OFTEN.
WHERE DID YOU COME BY
SOMETHING LIKE THAT?
HEY MAN, I HEARD YOU WERE
PISSING IN THEIR
POT PRETTY GOOD.
HE'S SURE GOT SOME BALLS
BEATING UP THE ORGANO'S HOODS
TO DEATH BY HIMSELF.
- Shinji:
GOT A PROPOSITION FOR YOU.
WHY DON'T YOU JOIN US?
I GUARANTEE YOU WON'T
REGRET IT.
YOU DO KNOW NOW THAT YOU'RE
THE SAME AS US,
RIGHT?
- HUH?
- WHAT IS IT?
- Sakimura: SKIRMISHES BETWEEN
THE ORGANO AND THE UNION
HAVE BECOME A CONTINUAL PROBLEM.
RIGHT NOW THEY'RE
ON A TEMPORARY TRUCE
SINCE ONISHI HAD
A FACE-TO-FACE NEGOTIATION
WITH THE UNION'S KIMATA.
BUT THE LOW-LEVEL MEMBERS
ARE AS HIGHLY VOLATILE AS EVER.
THINGS COULD ERUPT
AT ANY GIVEN MOMENT.
SHIN-SHIN-SE-KU-SA!
- ( whimpering )
- ( gun cocks )
- ( gun shot )
- Tsujinaka: HOW DID HE
COME OUT OF IT IN ONE PIECE?
- Organo member one:
NOT EXACTLY IN ONE PIECE.
HE'S NO LONGER A MAN.
- Tsujinaka:
HMM, I GUESS IT'D BE POINTLESS
TO TEXHNOLYZE THAT
PART OF THE BODY.
- Izaki:
WELL ON THE OTHER HAND,
THE WOMEN MIGHT LIKE
THAT BETTER.
- Organo member two:
WITH ALL THAT JERKY MOVEMENT.
- ( all laughing )
- Onishi:
IT'S NO LAUGHING MATTER.
IS IT THAT THEY'RE TRYING
TO SPIT IN THE ORGANO'S FACE?
OR IS IT THAT
THEY'RE UNABLE TO CONTROL
THEIR MORONIC HENCHMEN?
OR PERHAPS IT'S THE WORK
OF SOME OTHER PARTY.
- WHATEVER, IT'S A
GOOD OPPORTUNITY FOR US.
- NOW WE HAVE
THE PERFECT EXCUSE
TO COMPLETELY
DISSOLVE THE UNION.
- HM.
- Sonoda: THE YOUNG ONES ARE
ALL FIRED UP AS IT IS NOW.
- Tsujinaka: THE DISCONTENT
OF THE MEN BELOW US
HAS NOT BEEN RESOLVED,
THAT'S MORE OF A PROBLEM.
WHY DON'T WE DO IT AND LET
THEM BLOW OFF SOME STEAM.
- YES, MY FATHER IS
OF THE SAME OPINION.
THAT MUST BE
THE HAND OF FATE GUIDING US.
- CALL THE UNION, NOW.
- ( all groan )
- JUST FORGET IT.
YOU GO TO THE UNION AND DEMAND
AN ANSWER DIRECTLY FROM THEM
WHETHER OR NOT THIS INCIDENT
WAS TRULY THEIR DOING.
YOU WILL GO THERE
AS MY PERSONAL REPRESENTATIVE.
TELL THEM THAT THEIR
ATTITUDE TOWARDS YOU
IS THE SAME AS THEIR
ATTITUDE TOWARDS ME.
- YES SIR.
- I'VE MET WITH THEIR LEADER,
KIMATA.
HE DOESN'T STRIKE ME
AS BEING SO STUPID.
- ( jazz music playing )
- ( trembling )
- WELL, IT JUST TAKES
A LITTLE GETTING USED TO.
I REALLY DON'T CARE
HOW MANY GLASSES YOU BREAK.
GO AHEAD AND PRACTICE
ALL YOU WANT.
ONCE YOU LEARN THE
SLIGHT DIFFERENCES
BETWEEN CONSISTENCIES,
THEN SOME OF THE ANNOYING
THINGS FLOATING AROUND
SHOULD DISAPPEAR
FROM YOUR VISION.
- HUH?
- ( breathing heavily )
- YOU GUYS MAKE
A PRETTY GOOD TEAM.
- WHAT'S UP WITH YOU?
HOW COME YOU'RE BEING
SUCH A NICE GUY TODAY?
- HE KILLED SEVERAL
OF THE ORGANO'S HOODS
AND THEN CAME BACK FROM IT ALIVE
AS IF NOTHING HAD HAPPENED.
HE'S GOT SOMETHING ON HIM,
I'M NOT SURE WHAT IT IS YET.
BUT IT'S SOMETHING EVEN
THE ORGANO CAN'T TOUCH.
THE MORE CARDS WE'VE
GOT UP OUR SLEEVE,
THE BETTER OUR HAND.
- Sakimura: THERE WAS
AN INCIDENT RECENTLY.
A UNION SNIPER TRIED
TO SHOOT ONISHI.
THE UNION OFTEN EMPLOYS
TACTICS OF THAT SORT.
RUMOR HAS IT THAT IT WAS
THEM AS WELL WHO ATTEMPTED
THE ASSASSINATION OF
THE CHIEF OF GABE.
- ( gunshot )
- Izaki:
HAS IT BEEN CONFIRMED?
- Man:
YES, IT HAS.
- THAT'S THEIR REPLY.
WE'RE AT WAR.
- NOW ONISHI,
THE ONLY THING LEFT
IS FOR YOU TO MAKE UP YOUR MIND.
- NAKAHARA WAS KILLED ACTING ON
YOUR BEHALF, SO IT'S ON YOU.
- THE CITY DOES NOT WISH
FOR A SPECTACLE NOW.
- HUH?
- Onishi: AND THERE'S NO NEED
FOR US TO MAKE A MOVE YET.
- ( scowling )
- ( telephone ringing )
- THE ORGANO ARE PREPARING
FOR WAR.
THEY HAVE SENT WORD THAT THERE
IS NO ROOM FOR NEGOTIATION.
- AND WHAT ABOUT THOSE MEN
WHO ATTACKED THEM?
- WE'RE STILL INVESTIGATING.
- DO IT FAST.
- ( gunshot )
- IT WOULD SEEM
THAT THEY ARE SERIOUS.
- ONISHI.
- THE UNION HAS AN ULTIMATUM.
THERE'S NO ROOM
FOR NEGOTIATION.
- Onishi:
GIVE IT TO ME.
THIS IS ONISHI.
PUT KIMATA ON.
WHERE'S KIMATA?
- ( gasps )
WHO THE HELL ARE YOU?
I'M ORDERING YOU
TO IDENTIFY YOURSELF.
- Sakimura:
WHAT ARE YOU PLANNING TO DO?
- Yoshi:
DO, WHAT DO YOU MEAN?
- WELL, IT'S FINE IF YOU'RE JUST
GOING BACK QUIETLY, BUT--
- I HAVE NO INTENTION
OF GOING BACK QUIETLY.
THERE'S SO MUCH, MUCH MORE OF
THESE HUMAN'S PRIMITIVE ENERGIES
THAT I WANT TO SEE.
I GUESS YOU COULD SAY,
I'M STAYING. ( laughs )
- (panting) NAKAHARA'S MEN
COULDN'T STAND WAITING ANYMORE,
THEY, THEY, THEY--
- THEY WHAT?
- Yoshii:
YOU'RE TOO LATE.
MUCH TOO LATE, MR. ONISHI.
- ( gasps )
- THEY'RE ALL FOOLS.
- YOSHII.
- ( men screaming )
- CHANCELLOR, THIS WAY.
CHANCELLOR.
- ( men cheering )
- THAT'S THE WAY, JUST FIGHT.
FIGHT UNTIL YOU
CRUSH EACH OTHER.
- JUST FIGHT AND FIGHT,
THAT'S EXACTLY IT, SHINJI.
- ( theme music plays )
- ( singing in Japanese )