- Man: IF THERE'S
ANYTHING YOU WANT,
ANYTHING AT ALL,
COME TO ME.
I'M YOUR GUARDIAN ANGEL.
- ( theme music playing )
- Man: I CAN'T FORGET
ABOUT THAT TIME.
THE CITY FOLKS' EYES
CHANGED COLORS.
NO, IT'S NOT A FIGURE
OF SPEECH, NOT AT ALL.
THEIR EYES DID CHANGE COLORS.
AND THAT'S A FACT.
THIS PLACE WAS SHUT DOWN
FOR A FULL FIVE DAYS.
EH?  SIX DAYS?
THAT'S WHAT I SAID?
DID I NOW?  OH, WELL.
THE FOLKS UP IN THE MOUNTAIN
WERE RELATIVELY CALM,
BUT THE CITY WENT
INTO THIS MAD TURMOIL.
IT WAS BEYOND BELIEF.
SO THIS JUST GOES TO SHOW
THAT NO MATTER HOW UNNATURAL
AND UNREASONABLE
IT MAY SEEM TO YOU,
THE WORK WE DO HERE
IS IMPORTANT TO THOSE
WHO LIVE IN LUX.
YOU UNDERSTAND.
YOU KNOW WHAT I'M SAYING.
THE COLORS OF THEIR EYES
WERE DIFFERENT,
BUT YOU KNOW,
THE COLOR OF THE CITY
FOLKS' EYES,
WELL, MAYBE IT WASN'T
THE FIRST TIME
THEY HAD CHANGED.
- ( laughs )
YES, THAT'S RIGHT.
- ( door opens and closes )
- ( continues laughing )
YES.  I UNDERSTAND.
THANK YOU FOR LETTING ME KNOW.
MY HUSBAND IS UP NOW,
SO... YES.
YES, GOOD DAY.
- SO WHO ARE YOU SPEAKING TO?
- THE CITY.
- HMM?
- I WAS HAVING A CONVERSATION
WITH THE CITY.
BECAUSE IT'S NOT FAIR
THAT ONLY YOU CAN.
- THAT ONLY I CAN?
- THE CITY TALKS TO YOU,
DOESN'T IT?
YOU'RE VERY SPECIAL,
AREN'T YOU?
THAT'S WHY IT ISN'T FAIR.
- YOU HAVE A GOOD MEMORY.
IT WAS A LONG TIME AGO
WHEN I TOLD YOU ABOUT THAT.
BUT IT'S NOT AS IF IT TALKS
TO ME IN WORDS.
I THINK I TOLD YOU THAT AS WELL.
- ( beeps )
- BUT I KNOW THAT THE CITY
IS TALKING TO ME, TOO.
- ( telephone ringing )
- ( camera shutter clicking )
- Yoshii: AFTER ALL,
WE ALL BREATHE THE SAME AIR.
COME ON OVER HERE,
EVERYBODY.
WISHES DO GET HEARD, I GUESS.
UH-OH.
HUH?
- NO ONE CAN SAY THAT.
I'M NOT JUST A--
- ( engine revving )
- I WON'T LET THEM.
- ( telephone ringing )
- MICHIKO, ANY REPORTS
ON THE PACKAGE
FOR WHICH WE INITIATED
THE SEARCH?
- NO, NOT AS OF YET, SIR.
- WHICH ONES FROM TSUJINAKA'S
OFFICE ARE ON THE JOB NOW?
- TAKABE, MASHIMO AND ISHII,
I BELIEVE.
- ISHII.
BRING HIM TO ME
- ( shouting )
- YOU DON'T HAVE ANYTHING
TO REPORT?
- YOU WOULD HAVE HEARD IT
IF THERE WAS.
THERE'S NOTHING.
I MEAN IT.
I DON'T SEE WHY WE'RE DOING
ALL THIS
FOR THAT LITTLE SCUM.
- DO YOU KNOW WHETHER
HE'S SCUM OR NOT?
- HUH?
- IF HE REALLY IS SCUM,
THEN YOU ARE THE ONE
WHO MADE HIM LIKE THAT.
- THANK YOU VERY MUCH
FOR YOUR CONCERN.
GIVE MY REGARDS
TO MR. TSUJINAKA.
- ( panting )
- THIS IS SUPPOSED TO BE MY LEG.
- YOU ARE?
- MY NAME IS YOSHII.
HOW DO YOU DO?
THAT FOOT OF YOURS LOOKS
LIKE IT'S IN PAIN.
( laughs ) I FORGOT.
YOU'RE THE DOCTOR, NOT ME.
- NEVER SEEN YOU BEFORE.
ARE YOU WITH THE ORGANO?
ONISHI'S THE ONLY ONE
I MAKE CONTACT WITH.
- YEAH, THAT'S WHAT I'VE HEARD
ABOUT YOU.
- SO WHO ARE YOU?
- IN THE BEGINNING,
YOU WERE ON THE OTHER SIDE
OF THE GATES.
I REALLY DO LIKE YOU.
- TELL ME.
WHO THE HELL ARE YOU?
- IT CHEATS
THE IMMUNOLOGICAL RESISTANCE
IN NORMAL TRANSPLANTATION
BETWEEN INDIVIDUALS,
AS IF ASSIMILATION WAS MEANT
TO HAPPEN FROM THE BEGINNING.
ALL THANKS TO RAFFIA,
A KIND OF MOSS THAT CAN ONLY
BE COLLECTED IN THE CENTER
OF THIS CITY.
- WHERE ARE YOU FROM?
- RAFFIA.
THAT'S WHAT GAVE THIS CITY
IT'S RAISON D'ETRE.
THANKS TO IT, WE--
THE HUMAN SPECIES--
THAT MAY HAVE OTHERWISE
GONE EXTINCT LONG AGO,
CAN CONTINUE TO EXIST.
IT MAY BE A VERY
UNNATURAL MEANS.
NONETHELESS,
IT WAS DISCOVERED HERE.
I WONDER IF IT WAS GIVEN
TO US BY GOD
TO LET US KNOW THAT WE HUMANS
WERE ALLOWED
TO CONTINUE EXISTING, DOC.
- ACTUALLY, MY FOOT DOES HURT.
- HOW'D IT GO?
- WHO THE HELL DOES ONISHI
THINK HE REALLY IS?
- YOU DIDN'T COME HERE
FROM OUTSIDE THE GATES
WITH A NOBLE CAUSE OF GIVING
GOD'S BLESSING
TO NOT ONLY THE PEOPLE
WHO LIVE ABOVE GROUND,
BUT ALSO THOSE WHO LIVE
IN THE CITY,
OR PERHAPS YOU DID.
- THE CLASS IS STILL
IN A FASHION THE RULING PARTY
OF THIS WORLD.
I DON'T KNOW WHAT IT IS
YOU'RE TRYING TO FIND OUT.
BUT YOU'RE ONE OF THOSE
THAT CAN GO THROUGH THE GATES,
AREN'T YOU?
- I KIND OF LIKE
BEING HERE.
IT MAY BE THE FIRST TIME
I SEE HUMANS
BEHAVING SO HUMAN.
- I DON'T LIKE IT.
EITHER INSIDE OR OUTSIDE.
- A GODDESS WITH THE POWER
TO MECHANIZE HUMANS.
I SEE.
- BECAUSE THAT'S THE ONLY
REMAINING ROAD LEFT
TO EVOLUTION.
RAFFIA WASN'T DISCOVERED JUST
TO TRANSPLANT ONE HUMAN'S
ORGANS TO ANOTHER.
- THAT'S BEAUTIFUL.
- Man:
WHICH ONE DO YOU WANT?
WHICH ONE?  HUH!
( screaming )
- ( laughing )
HUH?
YOU, GET OUT OF MY WAY!
( screams )
- ( telephone ringing )
- LOOK, SON, IF YOU GOT
NOTHING ELSE TO DO,
WHY DON'T YOU STAY
IN THIS MARKET?
THOSE RACAN PUNKS ARE
REALLY GETTING
"STICKY FINGER" THESE DAYS.
HONESTLY,
I'M PAYING FOR PROTECTION,
BUT THEM GUYS
IN THEIR FANCY SUITS
DON'T EVER DO A THING FOR ME.
- WE'VE JUST RECEIVED WORD
FROM THE AZAKI OFFICE
THAT A MAN BELIEVED TO BE
OUR PACKAGE IS IN THE MARKET.
- REMIND THEM ONCE AGAIN
NOT TO KILL HIM.
- ( screams )
- TEN YEARS AGO ONISHI
WAS JUST A PUNK.
( grunts )
- WAIT. STOP THE CAR!
- ( tires screech )
- ( panting )
- ISHII,
YOU BETTER NOT DO IT NOW.
IF YOU KILL HIM, YOU'RE GONNA
BE PUTTING ALL OF US
IN A VERY AWKWARD POSITION.
- THIS GUY MAKES ME SICK.
I'LL CUT OFF THE REST
OF HIS LIMBS
AND THEN ONISHI CAN HAVE HIM.
WHAT THE HELL KIND OF
LOOK IS THAT?
YOU'RE DISGUSTING.
I HATE YOUR TYPE
BECAUSE YOU ACT LIKE
YOU'RE BETTER THAN EVERYONE,
THINKING YOU COULD
LIVE ON YOUR OWN,
BUT YOU'RE NOTHING BUT SCUM.
- ( panting )
- BECAUSE I USED
TO BE JUST LIKE HIM.
- ( grunts )
- ( rings )
( beeps )
- SO THEY FINALLY FOUND YOU.
I DON'T WANT YOU TO DIE,
NOT NOW.
- ( grunting )
- ( groans )
- ( yells )
- GOOD BOY, GOOD BOY.
- D-DAMN!
- ( clicks )
- DAMN YOU!
- ( gagging )
( coughs )
- ( thuds )
- ( grunts )
- Man:
WAY WAY BACK THEN,
I THINK EVERYBODY
HAD EYES LIKE THOSE.
HUH?  YOU'VE ALREADY HEARD
ME SAY THAT TO YOU
MANY TIMES BEFORE?
BUT THAT'S OKAY.
SO WE WON'T FORGET, RIGHT?
YOU KNOW...
- ( theme music playing )
- ( singing in Japanese )