- Man: IF THERE'S
ANYTHING YOU WANT,
ANYTHING AT ALL,
COME TO ME.
I'M YOUR GUARDIAN ANGEL.
- ( theme music playing )
- Man: I COULD SIMPLY CONTINUE
TO LIVE AS I HAVE,
BUT I'VE GROWN WEARY OF IT.
MOTHER AND THE OTHERS,
THEY DON'T SEE ANYTHING
OR SAY ANYTHING.
OH, WHAT'S THE MATTER?
IS IT THAT YOU WANT
MY LOVE AGAIN?
THEN YOU SHALL HAVE IT.
- WHY DID YOU DO IT?
AS I WATCHED YOU
MURDER THOSE MEN,
IT WAS AS IF YOU
HADN'T CHANGED AT ALL
FROM WHO YOU WERE BEFORE.
IF THAT'S SO, THEN HAVE
YOU GIVEN UP ON YOURSELF?
- NO, I HAVEN'T.
- ALL RIGHT.
I'VE ALREADY LECTURED TO YOU
ABOUT EVERYTHING THAT
I SHOULD HAVE.
NOW THE REST IS UP TO YOU.
NO, MAYBE I SHOULD SAY
IT'S UP TO MR. ONISHI.
AT ANY RATE,
MY CONGRATULATIONS
TO THE FULL SCALE REOPENING
OF THE ONISHI OFFICE
AND TO YOUR BECOMING
AN OFFICIAL MEMBER.
HERE IS MY LAST PIECE
OF ADVICE FOR YOU.
- I'VE BROUGHT YOU THE COMPLETE
REPORTS ON THE RECENT SERIES
OF DISTURBANCES.
THE OFFICE MANAGER REQUESTS
THAT YOU REVIEW THEM
JUST TO MAKE SURE.
- IT'S JUST THE SAME OLD THINGS.
- THAT'S BECAUSE THERE'S NOTHING
NEW WRITTEN IN THESE REPORTS.
- THEN WHY BRING THEM
TO ME?
- JUST A FORMALITY.
- ( sighs )
- MR. IWATA ASKED ME WHY
YOU WERE GOING TO GABE
AT A TIME LIKE THIS.
- I'M GOING THERE BECAUSE
IT IS A TIME LIKE THIS.
TELL HIM THAT.
- I HAVE ALREADY TOLD
MR. IWATA THAT.
- FINE THEN.
I NEED SOME TIME ALONE.
- YES, SIR.
- WHOOPS.
- NOW WHAT?
- ( laughs )
I DON'T NEED YOUR PERMISSION
TO SIT HERE.
WANT SOME?
YOU KNOW THAT YOU'RE
REALLY LUCKY.
MAKING SO MUCH TROUBLE
LIKE THAT,
YOU WOULD HAVE BEEN CONSIDERED
TOO MUCH OF A BURDEN
AND DECLARED EXPENDABLE
BY ANY OTHER OFFICE.
ALTHOUGH BEING
AS OLD AS I AM,
I WOULD HAVE GOTTEN THE AXE
AT ANY OTHER OFFICE.
SO I GUESS WE BOTH MADE
THE RIGHT CHOICE
WHEN WE DECIDED
TO WORK FOR HIM. ( laughs )
- IF YOU CONTINUE
TO SIT THERE LIKE THAT,
YOU WILL CATCH A COLD.
PLEASE, FINISH UP QUICKLY, RAN.
LET'S GO.
YOUR SITTING HERE AND HESITATING
TO FULFILL YOUR DUTY
WILL NOT CHANGE A THING.
- ( hydraulic brakes hiss )
- THIS PLACE HASN'T CHANGED
AT ALL.
- THAT'S ONLY BECAUSE
IT CAN'T CHANGE.
COMPARED TO THE CITY,
THIS PLACE MUST BE VERY BORING.
- THE CITY DOESN'T CHANGE,
EITHER.
AND THAT PLACE
IS FAR MORE VICIOUS.
- I HEARD YOU RECENTLY
LOST YOUR WIFE.
- YES.
- MY DEEPEST CONDOLENCES.
- Sage: THE VOICE OF THE CITY
HAS STOPPED.
- Onishi: YES, IT'S NOT AS IF
THE VOICE OF THE CITY
IS SOMETHING THAT
I CAN HEAR AT WILL.
BUT IT HAS BEEN SILENT
TOO LONG.
I FEEL AS THOUGH THE CITY'S
WILL HAS RECEDED.
- AND THAT'S WHY YOU DECIDED
TO MAKE THE JOURNEY HERE.
- BECAUSE OF AN OUTSIDER'S
INTERFERENCE,
THE CITY HAS FALLEN
INTO DISORDER.
- I AM VERY SORRY.
AS A RESIDENT OF GABE,
THERE IS NO ADVICE I CAN GIVE.
EVER SINCE OUR ANCESTORS
BUILT THE CITY LONG AGO,
SIMILAR INCIDENTS HAVE TAKEN
PLACE COUNTLESS TIMES.
A CITY IS BORN.
EVENTUALLY IT IS DESTROYED.
THE DESTROYER OF THE CITY
IS IN TURNED DESTROYED
AND THE CITY IS REBORN AGAIN.
ULTIMATELY, THE CYCLE
REPEATS ITSELF.
THAT IS THE WAY OF THE CITY.
- ARE YOU SAYING THAT THIS
HAS ALWAYS BEEN INEVITABLE?
- IT IS.
THE RESIDENTS OF GABE
HAVE DECIDED TO LIVE
KNOWING THIS INEVITABILITY.
- IS THERE ANY WAY LEFT FOR US?
- THERE MAY BE A WAY,
BUT YOU'LL NOT FIND IT
IN LUX.
THAT IS
IF YOU'RE STILL WILLING
TO RECEIVE ADVICE.
- HUH?
- SO YOU HAVE AN APPRECIATION
FOR THE BEAUTY OF FLOWERS.
SO TELL ME,
WHY ARE YOU IN THE ORGANO?
- WHAT DO YOU MEAN?
- YOU LOOK UNCOMFORTABLE.
YOU SEEM TO BE MORE COMFORTABLE
ACTING AS A LONER.
BUT YOU LOOK REALLY OUT
OF PLACE IN AN ORGANIZATION.
I'M NOT MAKING FUN OF YOU.
IT'S JUST ADVICE.
A GUY LIKE YOU DOESN'T SEEM
HE'D BE HAPPY BEING
PART OF THE ORGANO.
IF YOU WANNA GO,
THEN GO.
THE LONGER YOU STAY,
THE MORE DIFFICULT IT GETS
TO LEAVE.
DON'T GET ME WRONG.
I'M NOT TRYING TO FIGHT YOU.
I HAVE NOTHING AGAINST YOU.
THAT'S WHY I'M SAYING THIS.
- HMM?
- WHAT IS IT THAT
YOU WISH TO SEE?
- THIS MAN'S FUTURE.
AND THE FUTURE OF THE CITY
OF LUX.
- THE SEER WILL SPEAK
TO YOU NOW.
- YOU.
YOU ARE IN DANGER
OF BEING DESTROYED
BY WHAT YOU LOST
IN THE PAST.
YOUR LEGS.
YOUR LEGS
BEING DESTROYED.
COLLAPSING.
BOTH THE CITY AND HE.
- AND WHO?
- I DON'T WANNA SEE ANYMORE.
- Sage: A FEMALE CHILD WHO HAS
THE ABILITY TO SEE IS BORN
INTO EVERY GENERATION
WITHIN GABE.
SHE SEES THE FUTURE
OF EVERYTHING,
EVEN WHEN SHE DOESN'T WISH TO.
THAT IS A SEER.
WE ABIDE BY THE WORDS
OF THE SEER
BECAUSE THEY TELL US
OF OUR FUTURE.
HOWEVER, THIS GIRL HAS NOT
ACCEPTED SUCH
A GRAVE RESPONSIBILITY YET.
SHE CAN'T ACCEPT THE FUTURE THAT
SHE SEES FOR OTHER PEOPLE
AND FOR HERSELF.
- FINDING ANY PERSON WHO IS
CAPABLE OF ACCEPTING SUCH THINGS
AS FATE AND DESTINY SO EASILY
IS VERY RARE,
IS IT NOT?
- YOUR WORDS ARE NOT THE
LANGUAGE OF THE PEOPLE OF GABE,
BUT OF YOUR PEOPLE.
WHAT IS IT?
- HE WANTED ME TO TELL YOU
THAT HE SAW A SUSPICIOUS MAN
LURKING INSIDE THE FACTORY
JUST BEFORE.
- A SUSPICIOUS MAN?
- AND THAT A LARGE QUANTITY
OF SMALL ARMS
ARE BEING MANUFACTURED
INSIDE.
- GREAT SAGE.
MAY I PLEASE BE ALLOWED
TO SEE IT?
WHO ARE THESE FOR?
YOUR SILENCE IS NOT AN ANSWER.
NOW I SEE.
- ( grunting )
- ( screaming )
- ( gunshot )
- Man: I'M VERY SORRY, SIR.
I HAD NO TIME TO THINK.
- NEVER MIND ABOUT THAT.
AFTER ALL, YOU DID SAVE HIM.
- Sage:
DOES THIS MEAN THAT GABE
AND THE UNION ARE
SOMEHOW CONNECTED?
- Onishi: THE QUESTION IS,
WHO NEEDS SUCH A LARGE QUANTITY
OF WEAPONS?
IT'S UNLIKELY THAT
THE UNION COULD AFFORD IT.
THE SAME GOES WITH THE RACAN.
IT'S ALSO UNLIKELY THAT
GABE ITSELF IS IN NEED OF THEM.
SO WHAT WOULD YOU DO
IF YOU WERE ME?
- GO ASK THEM DIRECTLY.
- TELL ME, WHY DO YOU
EVEN BOTHER WITH ME?
- BECAUSE YOU'RE ONE
OF MY MEN NOW.
I CAN'T ALLOW YOU TO ACT IN SUCH
A RECKLESS MANNER ANYMORE.
AND I OWE YOU.
- BUT STILL,
THAT MUST BE A PAIN.
- IT'S A MATTER OF PROTOCOL.
AS LONG AS YOU'RE A MEMBER
OF THE ORGANO,
EVERYTHING YOU DO REFLECTS
UPON THE ORGANIZATION.
I WILL NOT HAVE YOU GO AROUND
KILLING PEOPLE
WITHOUT MY PERMISSION.
EVEN IF IT IS TO AVENGE
YOUR FATHER'S DEATH.
QUIT ACTING EMOTIONALLY.
YOU MUST LEARN
TO START USING YOUR HEAD.
- WHAT ABOUT YOUR LEGS THEN?
YOU LOST THEM BECAUSE YOU WERE
BEING RECKLESS, WEREN'T YOU?
- ( sighs )
I SOLD THEM.
IT'S NOT THE SAME.
WHEN I WAS A KID,
THERE WAS A BOY
WHO'D BEEN BORN
WITHOUT NORMAL LEGS,
AND THEY'D MADE AN OFFER
TO BUY LEGS FOR HIM
FROM A CHILD OF A SIMILAR AGE.
IT FELT ALMOST LIKE I WAS BEING
PRESSURED INTO DOING IT,
BUT I ALONE MADE THE DECISION.
STILL, I WAS JUST A KID.
I WAS TOO NAIVE.
I SOLD MY LEGS
TO PAY FOR MY NAIVETE.
BUT NOW I THINK IT WAS
FOR THE BEST.
WITHOUT THE LEGS I HAVE,
I WOULD NOT HAVE BEEN ABLE
TO HEAR THE VOICE OF THE CITY,
AND I WOULD NOT BE WHO I AM.
THESE ARE NOT JUST A SUBSTITUTE
FOR MY LEGS.
THESE ARE MY LEGS.
YOU SHOULD MAKE YOUR LIMBS
TRULY YOUR OWN AS WELL.
DWELLING ON THE PAST
ISN'T HEALTHY.
- PLEASE GET OUT,
BOTH OF YOU.
- WHY?
- THAT UNION MAN
WHO WAS SNEAKING AROUND
WAS AN UNEXPECTED ELEMENT.
- ARE YOU SAYING YOU KILLED HIM
ON PURPOSE?
- I DID.
- WHO DID YOU SELL OUT TO?
- WELL, IF I COULD
TELL YOU THAT,
I WOULDN'T HAVE TO KILL YOU
LIKE THIS.
BUT IF YOU HAVE TO KNOW,
IT'S A LITTLE MORE SECURE GROUP
TO BE IN THAN THE ORGANO.
I'M NOT SO YOUNG ANYMORE.
I HAVE NO FUTURE CLINGING
TO THE ORGANIZATION.
AT THIS POINT IN MY LIFE, IT
SEEMS LIKE A GOOD TURNING POINT.
- YOU KNOW, IT'S FUNNY.
I NEVER BELIEVED IN LOYALTY.
- BECAUSE YOU ARE WHO YOU ARE,
I NEVER DISLIKED YOU.
- ( gun cocks )
- AND YOU, BOY, REMEMBER.
I TRIED TO WARN YOU.
LEAVE THE ORGANO
WHILE YOU STILL CAN.
MR. ONISHI,
IT'S UNFORTUNATE.
- ( grunts )
- OH!
- TALK.
TELL ME WHO BOUGHT YOU OFF.
- ( grunts )
- WHO IS THE ONE
WHO BOUGHT YOU OFF?
HUH?
- MR. ONISHI, IT'S YOUR
CONTINUAL WEAKNESS
THAT COULDN'T BRING YOURSELF
TO KILL ME.
- TELL ME WHAT THIS
IS ALL ABOUT.
- Sage: UNFORTUNATELY,
IT IS NOT YET TIME,
FOR YOU TO KNOW WHAT
THIS IS ALL ABOUT.
MR. ONISHI, YOU WILL UNDERSTAND
WHEN THE TIME IS RIGHT.
BUT I WILL TELL
YOU ONE THING NOW.
WE ABIDE BY NOTHING OTHER
THAN THE WORDS OF THE SEER.
AND NO ONE ELSE.
- RAN.
- THAT IS EVERYTHING THAT
WE CAN TELL YOU FOR NOW.
LEAVE.  YOUR COMPANIONS
ARE WAITING AT THE STATION.
- RAN.
RAN.
- THE FUTURE.
THE ONE THAT I SAW FOR YOU,
IN THE END,
YOU WILL DESTROY EVERYTHING.
YOU WILL HURT MANY PEOPLE.
YOU WILL BE ALL ALONE
IN THE END.
- ( sighing )
NEVER.
I WON'T DO IT.
I CAN'T.  I CAN'T.
I'LL NEVER END UP
BEING LIKE THAT.
- I WISH.
I WISH THAT COULD BE SO.
BUT THE THINGS THAT I'VE SEEN
ARE BEGINNING TO COME TRUE.
- WAIT, RAN.
RAN!
- Man: IT HAS ALREADY BEGUN.
PLEASE WATCH ME,
MY DEAR SISTER.
- ( theme music playing )
- ( singing in Japanese )