- Man: IF THERE'S
ANYTHING YOU WANT,
ANYTHING AT ALL,
COME TO ME.
I'M YOUR GUARDIAN ANGEL.
- ( theme music playing )
- ( laughs )
- ( panting )
- ( wails )
- Woman: PLEASE, DON'T LOOK.
- ICHISE.
- ( music over sound )
- Yoshii: WHAT DO YOU DO WITH
THE MONEY FROM SELLING FLOWERS?
YOU'RE NOT AFRAID
OF THE CITY, ARE YOU?
IS IT A SAFE ENOUGH
PLACE FOR A GIRL
TO HANG OUT BY HERSELF?
I'M INDEBTED TO YOU
AND YOUR GRANDFATHER.
SO I'LL DO WHATEVER I CAN
TO HELP YOU.
I UNDERSTAND THAT THIS WORLD
OF LUX IS A PLACE
COMPLETELY UNFAMILIAR TO ME,
BUT THAT'S ALL THE MORE REASON
WE SHOULD--
RAN, CAN I ASK YOU A FAVOR?
- WHAT?
- I HEARD THAT YOU
CAN SOMETIMES SEE
THE NEAR FUTURE.
ISN'T THAT RIGHT?
- ONLY ONE POSSIBLE FUTURE.
- YOU SAW MY FUTURE,
DIDN'T YOU?
I DON'T WANT YOU
TO TELL ANYONE
ABOUT MY FUTURE,
ESPECIALLY ME.
- ( ringing )
- ( alarm beeping )
- ( beeping stops )
- ( sighs )
- WATER.
WATER.
- YOU SHOULD SAY PLEASE.
- PLEASE.
- ( beeping )
- ( gasping )
- ( loud thud )
- ( grunts )
( panting )
- WHERE ARE YOU GOING?
YOU'RE NOT GOING BACK
TO THAT DUMP.
- ( wheels clacking )
- ( telephone ringing )
- OH, WOULD YOU?
MY HANDS ARE FULL.
- ONISHI.
- ( beeping )
- WHAT WERE YOU GOING TO DO
WITH IT
PRESERVED IN SUCH A WAY?
A MEMENTO?
DON'T TELL ME YOU THOUGHT
YOU COULD STILL REATTACH IT
TO YOUR BODY.
THE CELLS IN YOUR ARM
ARE LONG DEAD.
EVEN RAFFIA DOESN'T HAVE
THE POWER TO REATTACH
A MUMMIFIED BODY PART.
- ( grunts )
- ( gasping )
( gagging )
- RAFFIA.
- I'VE GOT NOTHING TO DO
WITH ANYTHING
INVOLVING RAFFIA.
- THE PLACE YOU LIVED IN
IS GONE.
IT WAS BURNT TO THE GROUND.
- WHERE IS IT?
TELL ME WHERE IT IS.
- WHY DON'T YOU JUST LOOK
RIGHT OVER THERE?
- ( gasps )
- HUH?
HMM.
- ( gasps )
- YOU WANNA WAGE A WAR
THAT BADLY?
WHAT IS IT THAT YOU HOPE
TO ACCOMPLISH?
DO YOU THINK YOU
CAN REPLACE THE ORGANO?
THE MAN THAT YOU WORSHIP
SO BLINDLY-- KIMATA.
DO YOU KNOW WHY
HE'S TEXHNOLYZED?
OR MAYBE YOU DIDN'T EVEN KNOW
THAT THE LEADER
OF YOU FLESH FUNDAMENTALISTS
IS A TEXHNOLYZE HIMSELF.
THE ONLY THING THAT KIMATA WANTS
IS THE RAFFIA.
HE'S NEVER HAD ANY INTENTION
OF DELIVERING
YOUR LIBERATION.
- ( whimpering )
( shouting )
- ( gunshot )
- ( gasps )
- WAKE UP AND SMELL THE WORLD.
IF YOU'RE GOING BY THE TEXTBOOK,
THEN...
OH, WELL, AND I JUST WENT
THROUGH THE TROUBLE
OF HAVING IT SERVICED.
- I BELIEVE IT WASN'T
BY ACCIDENT
THAT I PICKED YOU UP.
I FOR ONE THINK THAT IT'S BORING
TO KEEP REPRODUCING
THE SAME TECHNOLOGY
OVER AND OVER AGAIN.
WITH RAFFIA
AND TEXHNOLYZED LIMBS,
A HUMAN ONLY RECOVERS
THE PREVIOUS SHAPE
AND NOTHING MORE.
I'VE BEEN WANTING TO CREATE
A MORE UNIQUE CHEMISTRY
FROM THE COMBINATION.
- TELL ME.
WHERE IS IT?
- YOU SHOULDN'T EVEN WORRY
ABOUT IT.
IF I WERE TO BILL YOU FOR THE
OPERATION AT THE NORMAL RATE,
YOU COULDN'T POSSIBLY PAY
EVEN WITH AN ENTIRE LIFETIME
OF HARD LABOR.
- TELL ME.  WHERE IS IT?
- WELL, I DIDN'T THROW IT AWAY.
I'M ASKING YOU WHAT YOU DID
WITH IT.
WILL YOU TELL ME
WHO IT IS?
THOUGH I CAN GUESS.
I SEE THOSE EVERY NOW AND THEN.
PEOPLE WHO CAN'T EVEN AFFORD
TO BURY THEIR DEAD
IN A LOW INCOME CEMETERY.
USUALLY THEIR WIFE
OR HUSBAND.
GIRLFRIEND?  PROBABLY NOT.
YOUR MOTHER.
- ( gasps )
- SHE'S IN THERE.
I MERELY HAD HER PLACED
INSIDE THAT TEXHNOLYZE UNIT.
YOU MUST HAVE KNOWN
THAT KEEPING
ONLY CELLS ALIVE
IS ABSOLUTELY MEANINGLESS.
YOU KNEW IT,
BUT YOU COULDN'T HELP IT.
YOU COULDN'T GET RID OF IT.
AFTER ALL, IT'S YOUR MOTHER.
THAT UNIT HAS BECOME A LIVING
BEING AS IT WERE.
IT'S MORE THAN A MECHANISM
OPERATING IN COMBINATION
WITH THE NEUROTRANSMISSION
SYSTEM.
WHAT I HAVE DONE
IS UTILIZE YOUR MOTHER'S CELLS
AS THE BIOCIRCUIT.
- ( panting )
- THAT'S GOING TO
BE YOUR NEW ARM
AND YOUR NEW LEG.
I TOOK YOUR PRECISE MEASUREMENTS
WHEN I CREATED THOSE.
TEXHNOLYZED LIMBS ARE ALWAYS
ORDER MADE.
- NOW I SEE.
- WHAT DO YOU WANT TO DO?
BLOW THE OPPORTUNITIES
THAT ARE GIVEN TO YOU?
LIVE WITHOUT MEANING
AND DIE WITHOUT MEANING?
- BY HAVING A MECHANICAL ARM
AND LEG?
I DON'T NEED ANY
OF THOSE THINGS.
- FINE WITH ME, BUT YOU'RE
GOING TO TAKE THAT UNIT
DOWN WITH YOU.  YOU'RE GOING TO
KILL YOUR OWN MOTHER
WITH YOUR OWN HAND.  LOVELY.
- DAMN YOU!
( screaming )
( grunts )
- DOC, I TRIED TO ADVISE YOU
AGAINST DOING THIS,
DID I NOT?
I NEVER EXPECTED
TO SEE HIM AGAIN.
IT'S IRONIC BECAUSE HAD
I BEEN MORE MERCIFUL
AND PUT HIM OUT OF HIS MISERY
BACK WHEN WE FIRST MET,
HE WOULD NEVER HAVE BEEN
PICKED UP BY YOU.
- WHAT WAS THAT FOR?
YOU SHOW UP UNANNOUNCED AND KILL
HIM WITHOUT MY PERMISSION.
- I DID NOT CUT HIM.
I WOULD NEVER EVEN CONSIDER
DULLING MY BLADE
ON A MERE STRAY DOG.
- ( gasping )
- HE'S NOT DEAD.
- ALTHOUGH AN ORDINARY HUMAN
WOULD HAVE PROBABLY BEEN DEAD.
- TO HAVE SUCH AN OVERWHELMING
OBSESSION TO LIVE.
ISN'T IT REMARKABLE?
- I'M SORRY TO INTERRUPT WHAT
SEEMS LIKE YOUR GREAT AMUSEMENT,
BUT...
- HMM?
( laughs )
- ( breathing )
- ( theme music playing )
- ( singing in Japanese )