- Man: IF THERE'S
ANYTHING YOU WANT,
ANYTHING AT ALL,
COME TO ME.
I'M YOUR GUARDIAN ANGEL.
- ( theme music playing )
- ( techno music playing )
- ARE YOU BORED?
- HUH?
IT'S HARD FOR ME TO BE
IN A PLACE LIKE THIS.
MY EARS ARE A BIT--
MAYBE I'M JUST OLD.
ARE YOU BORED?
- THIS IS MY SPACE.
I CALL IT THE VIP ROOM.
- I'M SURPRISED YOU WOULD BE
ATTRACTED TO LIGHTS LIKE THESE,
OR OTHER THINGS.
- ( woman laughing )
YEAH, YOU CAN DO IT.
- HEY, ISN'T THAT YOUR
GIRLFRIEND OVER THERE?
DON'T YOU MIND?
- SHE'S FREE.
IT'S HER CHOICE.
- REALLY?
- WE DON'T BELONG
TO ANYONE OR ANYTHING.
WE'VE GATHERED TOGETHER OUT
OF OUR OWN FREE WILL.
THAT'S WHY WE'RE UNITED.
- HMM.
YOU'RE A PHILOSOPHER.
- I HEARD THAT YOU COME
FROM THE OUTSIDE WORLD.
SO TELL ME,
WHAT'S IT LIKE OUT THERE?
- WELL, WHY DON'T YOU GO SEE
FOR YOURSELF?
- IS THERE STILL
SOMETHING THERE?
- THERE PROBABLY IS
IF YOU THINK SO.
AND THERE PROBABLY ISN'T
IF YOU DON'T.
- DON'T ACT SO PRETENTIOUS.
- ANYTHING THAT'S REALLY FREE
CAN'T BE LEANING
ON ANYTHING ELSE.
IT'S WANDERING.
IT'S LONELY, AND IT'S ARDUOUS.
YOU CAN'T HOPE FOR
ANY SECURITY OR REWARD
BEYOND THE NAME.
- NO REWARD NEEDED.
JUST PROOF.
- THEN THOSE LIGHTS.
- YEAH.
- YOU JUST SAID THAT YOU DON'T
BELONG TO ANYTHING.
BUT THAT'S A LIE.
- HUH?
- BECAUSE YOU BELONG
TO THIS CITY.
AND I'M SURE SO DOES
YOUR FREEDOM.
SO TELL ME,
WHERE'S THERE
A NICE PLACE I CAN GO TO?
WHERE I CAN FIND SOME WOMEN THAT
ARE MORE APPROPRIATE FOR MY AGE?
- WELL, HE HASN'T BEEN FOUND
AS OF YET.
- Doc: HE DOESN'T HAVE
A TEXHNOLYZED LIMB EXTERIOR.
HOW CAN ANYONE MISS IT?
- Man: I'LL SEE TO IT
THAT MY MEN KNOW ABOUT THAT.
UNTIL THEN.
- ( sighs )
WHAT AN IMPOSSIBLE DOCTOR.
MAKES YOU WONDER WHICH ONE
OF US IS THE CLIENT.
- SHALL I INFORM THE MEN
TO MAKE SURE?
- LEAVE THEM ALONE.
SOMEONE WILL BE ABLE
TO FIND THEM SOONER OR LATER.
- I UNDERSTAND.
- USUALLY ONE BORN
WITH STUPIDITY
IS SUPPOSED TO BE CURED
WHEN THEY DIE.
- ( grunting )
GO AWAY!
( shouts )
- SO...
WHAT KIND OF GIRL
WOULD YOU LIKE, HUH?
( clears throat )
DON'T WANNA BE RUDE,
BUT YOU GOT ANY MONEY?
- YEAH, SURE.
- THE CUSTOMER'S OWN TOYS
AIN'T ALLOWED INSIDE.
SORRY, BUT YOU'RE GONNA HAVE
TO LEAVE THAT OUT HERE.
- I'M AFRAID THAT'S NOT GOOD.
- IF YOU'RE INTERESTED
IN THAT KIND OF PLAY,
THERE'S THIS GUY OUTSIDE.
HE CAN GET YOU SOMEONE.
( laughs )
ALTHOUGH I GOTTA TELL YOU,
THERE'S ONLY ONE GIRL
HE CAN GET YOU.
- ( gasps )
- SORRY.  YOU GOTTA GO.
HUH?
- I PREFER NOT TO BE TOUCHED
BY A MAN.
- ( sighs )
- Man: HEY, MISTER.
- HMM?
- COME HERE.  YOU LOOKING
FOR SOMETHING DIFFERENT, EH?
- YEAH, HOPEFULLY SOMEONE
WITH EXPERIENCE.
- ( laughs ) I'VE GOT JUST
THE RIGHT ONE FOR YOU.
HEY, COME OUT.
- HOW DO YOU DO?
- SHITHEAD!
I HATE STRAY DOGS.
I'LL KILL YOU IF I FIND YOU
FOOLING AROUND HERE AGAIN.
- ( laughing )
- Yoshii: SO YOU ARE
EXPERIENCED, AREN'T YOU?
EXCUSE ME FOR ASKING,
BUT I WONDER HOW OLD YOU ARE.
- DON'T MESS WITH ME.
YOU THINK I'M GONNA ANSWER THAT?
I DIDN'T LIKE YOU
THE MOMENT I LAID EYES ON YOU.
UGH! ( panting )
- YOU CAN DROP THE ACT.
I WON'T BE PROVOKED NO MATTER
HOW MUCH DIRT YOU THROW AT ME.
AND JUST SO YOU KNOW,
I DON'T HAVE A TASTE
FOR THAT KIND OF THING.
- WHAT IS IT THEN?
WHAT DO YOU WANNA DO?
- TO BE HONEST,
I JUST WANNA TALK WITH YOU.
- HUH.  THAT'S THE ONE
ONISHI WAS TALKING ABOUT.
- LOOK AT THOSE FANCY
NEW LIMBS HE HAS.
- ( laughing )
- ( panting )
- ( gasps )
- ARE YOU SURE ABOUT THIS?
- THIS SEWER IS A MAZE
HE'LL NEVER GET OUT OF.
JUST AFTER HE DIES
A WRETCHED DEATH,
SOME SUCK-UP TO ONISHI
WILL FIND HIM.
- Woman:
UP TO THE SECOND BRIDGE,
THAT'S THE TERRITORY
OF THE SALVATION UNION
LED BY KIMATA.
BEYOND THE END OF THE ROAD,
BY THE HILL IS THE RACAN'S
TERRITORY.
IT'S A NEUTRAL ZONE
AROUND HERE,
BUT BEYOND THIS
EVERYTHING BELONGS
TO THE BIGGEST ORGANIZATION
IN LUX-- THE ORGANO.
WILL THAT DO?
- YEAH, THAT HELPS A LOT.
IT'S PRETTY DIFFERENT.
DO YOU EVER MEET
THE ORGANO'S EXECUTIVES AS WELL?
- YEAH, RIGHT.  DO YOU THINK
THEY DEAL WITH SOMEONE LIKE ME?
- HMM.
- I SEE.
YOU'RE NOT FROM AROUND HERE,
ARE YOU?
- DO YOU WANT TO GO UP
TO THE SURFACE?
- YEAH, AND STRAIGHTEN
MY LIFE OUT.
- THEN WHY DON'T YOU?
- 'CAUSE I'D BE KILLED.
- ( sighs ) SO WHAT DOES
IT TAKE TO BECOME LIKE THAT?
- EVERY MAN RUNS OUT OF THE ROOM
AS SOON AS HE SEES THIS.
SO I CAN'T HAVE ANYONE DECENT.
HE WAS A SOMEBODY ONCE,
YOU KNOW,
BUT A RIVAL GANG GOT HIM
AND, WELL,
MADE HIS EQUIPMENT USELESS.
THEN HE DECIDED
HE COULDN'T STAND
THE THOUGHT
OF ME BEING NORMAL.
- Yoshii: IF YOU LEAVE HERE,
HE WON'T BE WITH YOU.
THEN WON'T YOU MISS HIM?
- MISS HIM? ( laughs )
YOU'VE GOTTA BE KIDDING.
I'D RATHER FIND SOMEONE
WHO DOESN'T KNOW ME.
IF THEY DON'T KNOW
I'M LIKE THIS,
THERE MIGHT BE
SOMEONE NICE OUT THERE.
WHO KNOWS?
I MIGHT EVEN GET LUCKY ENOUGH
TO MEET
SOMEONE NICE LIKE YOU.
- YOU ARE BEAUTIFUL.
- Woman: MY GOD.
- DON'T WORRY.
THIS IS JUST A PART OF MY BODY.
- ( panting )
( grunts )
( screams )
- DON'T WORRY.
YOU'LL BE FREE.
- ( laughing )
OH!
- Yoshii: THIS PLACE IS
DEFINITELY BRIMMING
WITH THE ENERGY TO LIVE,
BUT HALF-MEASURES WON'T DO.
- ( panting )
( grunting )
( screaming )
- ( theme music playing )
- ( singing in Japanese )