- Man: IF THERE'S
ANYTHING YOU WANT,
ANYTHING AT ALL,
COME TO ME.
I'M YOUR GUARDIAN ANGEL.
- ( theme music playing )
- Man: RAN.
THE DAY HAS COME AT LAST.
I WISH I COULD SEE YOUR FACE
ONE LAST TIME,
BUT MY WISH WILL NOT BE GRANTED.
I KNOW THOSE WHO
ARE BORN IN GABE,
ARE EXPECTED TO ACCEPT
THE SEER'S WORDS
WITHOUT RESERVATION YET.
NOW WHEN IT'S MY TURN
TO FACE DEATH,
I AM UTTERLY CONSUMED
WITH FEAR.
IT'S SHAMEFUL.
BUT PLEASE.
BE WITH ME IN
MY FINAL MOMENT, RAN.
IF MY DEATH IS
TO HAVE ANY MEANING--
- ( gunshot )
- SO KUGAYAMA HAS LEFT US.
- IT SEEMS SO.
- HIS DEATH MAKES THE SIXTH.
HAVE YOU NOTIFIED THE REMAINING
THREE ABOUT HIS PASSING?
- NOT YET, SIR.
- WHAT DO YOU MEAN NOT YET?
- WHAT I SAY NOW,
I SAY WITH ALL DUE RESPECT
TO YOU, GREAT SAGE.
EVEN THOUGH THINGS HAPPENING
HAVE BEEN FORETOLD BY THE SEER,
I CANNOT AGREE WITH THE IDEA
THAT WE MUST DO NOTHING
BUT SIT BACK AND WATCH
THE PEOPLE OF GABE BE MURDERED.
- IT IS WRONG OF YOU TO THINK
THAT THEY WERE MURDERED.
IT WAS SIMPLY
THE INEVITABLE FACT
THAT THEIR TIME HAD COME.
- BUT, SIR.
- THE WORDS OF THE SEER
FORESHADOW WHAT EVENTUALLY
BECOMES REALITY,
A REALITY WE HAVE NO ABILITY
TO EITHER AVOID OR ESCAPE.
YOU MUST GIVE UP THE FOLLY
OF TRYING
TO CHANGE WHAT MUST BE.
- SO YOU'RE SAYING THAT IF
THE SEER'S WORDS ARE EVER LOST
TO US, THEN REALITY WILL
BE LOST TO US AS WELL.
THAT IS HOW IT IS
ACCORDING TO YOUR LOGIC,
IS IT NOT?
WHICH IN TURN MEANS THAT
GIVEN THE CURRENT STATE
OF THE SEER, GABE IS COMPLETELY
LOST IN THE DARK
AS TO WHAT TO DO,
EVEN TODAY.
THEN I HAVE TO MAKE A REQUEST.
YOU MUST DO SOMETHING
ABOUT THE SEER.
- THE SEER IS STILL
MUCH TOO YOUNG.
SHE CANNOT ENDURE TO SEE WHAT
SHE DOES NOT WANT TO SEE.
EVENTUALLY, SHE WILL ACCEPT
HER POSITION IN THIS WORLD
AND ONLY THEN
WILL SHE SPEAK TO US
WHEN SHE IS WILLING.
- AND WHEN WILL THAT BE?
IF YOU CANNOT GIVE
US THAT ANSWER,
THEN WE REQUEST PERMISSION
TO ACT
REGARDLESS OF THE SEER'S WORDS.
- ( groans )
- TELL ME WHY.
WHY?
- Onishi:
WAIT FOR ME HERE.
- THE EXECUTIVE MEETING STARTS
AT 1:00.
- I KNOW.
- ( alarm sounding )
- ( gun cocks )
- WHAT DO YOU WANT?
- WHY DID YOU DISAPPEAR
ALL OF A SUDDEN?
- NO REASON.
IN FACT, I DON'T RECALL
EVER DOING SUCH A THING.
- IF YOU BECOME COMPLETELY
UNREACHABLE,
THEN IS THAT NOT THE SAME
AS DISAPPEARING?
I NEED TO KNOW EXACTLY
WHAT'S HAPPENING ON THE HILL.
DOC, I WANT YOU
TO TELL ME EVERYTHING RIGHT NOW.
- WHERE'S KAKU?
- UH...
UH...
- YOICHI AND THE OTHERS?
- DIDN'T YOU SEE THEM OUTSIDE?
MAYBE THEY'RE JUST HANGING
AROUND SOMEWHERE.
- HEY, GORO,
HOW MANY OF US ARE LEFT?
- I THINK THERE'S MORE THAN 20.
- YOU THINK?
- I HAVEN'T BEEN ABLE TO GET
A HOLD OF HITOSHI AND MARU
SINCE LAST NIGHT.
- I GET IT.
- WELL, MAYBE THEY'RE STILL
AT HOME JUST SLEEPING.
- YOKO.
- SHINJI.
- IF YOU WANT TO LEAVE,
THEN LEAVE.
YOU'RE FREE.
DO WHATEVER YOU WANT.
- WHY DO YOU HAVE TO SAY THAT,
SHINJI?
- I'LL TELL YOU THIS MUCH
AT LEAST.
DON'T PITY ME.
I WON'T TOLERATE IT.
NOT EVEN FROM YOU.
I DON'T THINK WE'D GAIN ANYTHING
BY BECOMING GOOD PALS
WITH THE GHOSTS.
BUT IF WE FIGHT AGAINST THEM,
IT'LL CERTAINLY BE A LOT
MORE TROUBLE THAN IT'S WORTH.
I DON'T LIKE THIS
SITUATION ONE BIT.
THIS THING COMPLETELY SUCKS!
- Man:
THIS ISN'T TREASON.
IT'S A DISILLUSIONMENT
OF OUR RELATIONSHIP
DUE TO AN IDEOLOGICAL
EVOLUTION.
WE'VE BEEN FORTUNATE ENOUGH
TO ENCOUNTER A GREATER BEING
WHO IS CAPABLE OF REALIZING OUR
IDEALS IN A MORE EVOLVED FORM.
AND THAT IS THE REASON
WE ARE LEAVING.
BUT THE REASON WE CHOOSE NOT
TO INVITE YOU TO COME WITH US
AT THIS TIME IS THAT WE HOPE
YOU WILL IDEOLOGICALLY EVOLVE
BY YOUR OWN ACCORD.
DO YOU UNDERSTAND WHAT IT IS
THAT I'M TRYING TO SAY?
THAT LEFT ARM OF YOURS.
I'VE KNOWN ABOUT IT
SINCE LONG AGO.
- WHAT YOU DON'T KNOW
IS BECAUSE I WAS TEXHNOLYZED
IT'S GIVEN ME THE CLARITY
TO GRASP THE EVILS
OF TEXHNOLYZATION.
TEXHNOLYZATION IS THE ENEMY
OF THE BODY.
IT AFFECTS THE BODY.
IT AFFECTS THE MIND.
AND EVENTUALLY, IT AFFECTS
THE MAN HIMSELF.
- AND YET, YOU COULD NOT PREACH
THE UNION IDEALS
THAT YOU VALUE SO DEARLY
WITHOUT HIDING YOUR LEFT ARM.
YOUR ACTIONS ARE LUDICROUS
AS WELL AS PATHETIC.
SUCH FLAWS IN MEN ARE WHAT
HE DESPISES THE MOST.
IT IS MY SINCERE
HOPE THAT ONE DAY
YOU WILL REALIZE
YOUR OWN IDEOLOGICAL
AND PHYSICAL VULNERABILITIES,
ASSUMING THAT YOU ARE WILLING.
I WILL TAKE SOME 60 MEN
WITH ME.
BELIEVE ME WHEN I SAY THAT
I HOPE YOU WILL ONE DAY
JOIN US IN OUR ACTIVITIES.
GOODBYE.
- IT'S NOT AS IF THESE THINGS
WERE JUST HAPPENING
ALL OF A SUDDEN.
IT'S JUST THAT WHAT HAS
ALWAYS BEEN THERE
IS NOW BECOMING MORE APPARENT.
- I THOUGHT YOU WERE SUPPOSED
TO BE TAKING PART IN IT
SINCE YOU'RE A MEMBER
OF THE CLASS.
- I THOUGHT I WAS,
BUT I GUESS I WAS WRONG.
- I WAS INVITED.
HE CAME TO ME AND TOLD ME
THAT I WOULD BE WISE
TO TAKE PART IN IT.
- SO YOU MET HIM.
YOU SAW WHO HE WAS.
- I DID NOT SEE HIS FACE,
BUT HE GAVE ME
SOME INSANE SPEECH.
I COMPLETELY REJECTED
HIS INVITATION OF COURSE.
NOW, DOC, YOU MUST TELL ME
WHO THAT MAN IS.
- BUT WILL YOUR KNOWING
CHANGE ANYTHING?
- HE SEEMED FAMILIAR.
I THINK I MIGHT HAVE MET HIM
SOMEWHERE BEFORE.
ALTHOUGH I CANNOT BE CERTAIN.
- YOU MUST BE SERIOUSLY
MISTAKEN.
EVEN WITHIN THE CLASS,
ONLY A SELECT FEW
ARE ALLOWED TO MEET
FACE-TO-FACE
WITH SOMEONE THAT HIGH UP.
- IS HE SERIOUS
ABOUT WHAT HE'S PLANNING?
- HE'S QUITE SERIOUS.
HE'S GOING TO REMAKE LUX
ACCORDING TO HIS OWN
CRAZY IDEOLOGY.
AND HE IS IN THE PROCESS
OF MAKING IT HAPPEN.
HE USED TO BE REGARDED
AS A HERETIC WITHIN THE CLASS,
BUT NOW BECAUSE OF HIM,
THE CLASS HAS TRIED
TO ELIMINATE MY IDEAS
BY ELIMINATING ME ENTIRELY.
THEIR MESSAGE IS CLEAR.
THEY NO LONGER HAVE ANY USE
FOR ME.
WHAT ARE YOU GOING TO DO?
NO MATTER WHAT YOU TRY,
THIS CITY IS GOING TO CHANGE.
NO ONE CAN STOP IT.
NOT EVEN YOU.
NOT ANYONE.
- I WANNA GET SOME FRESH AIR.
SINCE I'M GOING,
PERHAPS YOU SHOULD
COME ALONG WITH ME.
- Man: HOW'S THE ORGANO?
HOW ARE YOU FITTING IN?
( laughs )
YOU STILL DON'T LIKE
TO TALK MUCH, DO YOU?
BUT SEEING THAT YOU HAVEN'T
QUITTED AFTER ALL THIS TIME,
I SUPPOSE YOU CAN'T REALLY SAY
YOU HATE IT.
- I'M NOT SO SURE.
I'M NOT SURE AT ALL.
I'VE BEEN OFTEN ASKING MYSELF
WHY I'M HERE AS I AM NOW.
- Ran:
YOU WILL HURT MANY PEOPLE.
- ARE YOU WORRIED
ABOUT WHAT THE SEER SAID?
FORGET ABOUT IT.
WORDS ARE MERELY NOTHING
MORE THAN WORDS.
- BUT MY FUTURE.
- WHAT GOOD IS IT TO KNOW
ABOUT YOUR FUTURE?
ARE YOU GOING TO LIVE
EXACTLY LIKE THE PEOPLE OF GABE
AND JUST GIVE UP
ON EVERYTHING AND DO NOTHING?
OR WASTE YOUR LIFE AWAY
JUST LANGUISHING?
I DIDN'T WANNA DO EITHER.
THAT'S WHY I STAYED HERE
IN THE CITY INSTEAD
OF GOING TO GABE.
I FELT LIKE SHAPING
MY OWN FUTURE.
WHAT DO YOU WANT?
WHAT DO YOU WANNA DO, SON?
NOW GO AHEAD,
YOU CAN TELL ME.
- I'M NOT SURE.
- THE FIRST THING YOU SHOULD
DO IS TO FIND THAT OUT.
ONCE YOU'VE DONE THAT,
THEN THERE'S NOTHING
TO WORRY ABOUT.
THE ONLY THING LEFT
WILL BE TO GO OUT AND GET IT.
YOU NEED TO THINK ABOUT WHY
HE SENT YOU HERE TO SEE ME.
MORE IMPORTANTLY,
YOU NEED TO THINK ABOUT WHAT
HE REALLY WANTS FROM YOU,
FOR WHAT REASON
ARE YOU HERE GUARDING ME?
THINK ABOUT IT.
KEEP THINKING
AND SOONER OR LATER
THE SEER'S WORDS WILL
BECOME EMPTY IN MEANING,
AS THEY SHOULD.
- THERE'S A PROBLEM.
- HMM?
- I KNOW I'M LATE.
MY APOLOGIES.
- THERE'S NO WORRY.
ALTHOUGH THIS IS
A REGULAR MEETING,
THIS ONE WON'T TAKE LONG.
- WHAT DO YOU MEAN BY THAT?
- LET ME GET STRAIGHT
TO THE POINT.
THE ORGANO IS COMING TO AN END
AS OF TODAY.
FROM NOW ON,
THE CITY OF LUX WILL BE GOVERNED
DIRECTLY BY THE CLASS.
THEY'VE DESIGNATED ME
TO SERVE AS THEIR CONDUIT.
FROM NOW ON, YOU ARE TO FOLLOW
ALL MY INSTRUCTIONS
WITHOUT EXCEPTION.
THIS HAS BEEN ALREADY DECIDED
AND IS NOT A MATTER
FOR DISCUSSION.  THAT'S IT.
- THIS IS A COUP.
- I BELIEVE I GAVE YOU AMPLE
CLUES THAT THIS WAS COMING.
- HMM.
STILL AS A FORMALITY, WE MUST
TAKE A VOTE ON THE SUBJECT.
ALL THOSE WHO DO NOT ACCEPT
WHAT KOHAKURA SAID,
STAND UP.
- ARE YOU SURE ABOUT THIS?
- GREAT FATHER ONLY TOLD ME
THAT I SHOULD FOLLOW
YOUR DECISIONS, MR. ONISHI.
-  HOW DISAPPOINTING.
I WAS UNDER THE IMPRESSION
THAT YOU WERE DREAMING
THE SAME DREAM THAT I WAS.
THE NEXT TIME THAT WE MEET,
YOU'D BETTER NOT
TURN YOUR BACK ON ME.
- NOTHING SEEMED OUT
OF THE ORDINARY
UNTIL A FEW MINUTES AGO.
- WHAT THE HELL HAPPENED
IN HERE?
- SASAKI WENT TO CHECK IT OUT,
BUT STILL HASN'T RETURNED.
- WE'RE GOING BACK INSIDE THEN.
YOUNG MAN, IF YOU SEE THEM
COME BACK IN HERE,
KILL THEM
WITHOUT HESITATION,
BUT DO IT WITHOUT HARMING
THE OTHER PATIENTS.  UNDERSTOOD?
- THIS IS UNBELIEVABLE.
- IT WAS NO GOOD
INSIDE THE ROOM, SIR.
THEY WERE ALL KILLED--
- ( gunfire )
- ( gasping )
- ( grunts )
- WHAT?
- HUH?
- ( gasps )
- ( grunting )
- GET OUT OF MY WAY,
YOU BASTARD.
- ( whirring )
- All: HUH?
- GIVE IT UP.
YOUR TIME IS OVER.
- WE HAVE COME TO GET YOU,
SIR.
- Man: COMPLAINING?
WHAT ARE THEY COMPLAINING ABOUT?
- Boy: THEY'RE BORED BECAUSE
THE PEOPLE OF GABE
ARE NOT OFFERING
ANY RESISTANCE.
- TELL ME, WHO ARE THEY?
- MAINLY ONES WHO USED
TO BE MEMBERS OF THE RACAN.
- WELL, IF THAT'S THE CASE, WE
MUST DO OUR BEST TO HELP THEM.
DON'T JUST CUT OFF AN ARM
OR A LEG,
BUT ALL FOUR LIMBS
FROM EVERY ONE OF THEM
AND REPLACE THEM ALL
WITH NEW UNITS.
THEY MUST ONLY UNDERSTAND
MY IDEOLOGY.
BUT IT'S POINTLESS UNLESS
THEY PHYSICALLY
UNDERSTAND ME AS WELL.
- AS YOU WISH, SIR.
- HOW IRONIC THAT I'M GOING TO
GABE AFTER ALL THIS TIME.
- THIS CITY IS VERY DANGEROUS.
IF ANYTHING SHOULD HAPPEN
TO YOU NOW, THERE WILL BE
NO HOPE OF RESTORING THINGS
EVEN IF THERE IS STILL
HOPE OTHERWISE.
- KEIGO.
JUST GIVE UP THE ORGANO.
IT EXISTED MERELY
FOR THE SAKE OF CONVENIENCE.
IT DOESN'T MATTER IF IT'S TO BE
DISSOLVED AT THIS POINT.
IT'S MORE IMPORTANT THAT
YOU DO WHAT YOU HAVE TO.
YOU MAY USE ALL OF MY MEN
HOWEVER YOU LIKE.
- GREAT FATHER.
- YOUNG MAN.
I'LL BE SEEING YOU AGAIN.
- I MUST THANK YOU.
THAT WAS EXCELLENT WORK.
- BUT I-- ( gasps )
- HMM?
- Man: TO ALL OF YOU
WHO ARE CAPABLE
OF HEARING MY WORDS,
LISTEN TO ME.
I AM PLEASED TO TELL YOU
THAT LUX 100 YEAR HISTORY
OF BLOODSHED AND DISORDER
IS COMING TO AN END AT LAST.
AS OF TODAY,
LUX WILL BE GOVERNED
DIRECTLY BY US--
THE CLASS.
MY PEOPLE, DO NOT BE AFRAID.
OUR ULTIMATE GOAL IS
TO BUILD A BEAUTIFUL NEW
AND PROSPEROUS LUX.
WE WILL PROVIDE UNWAVERING
SUPPORT FOR YOU
TO OBTAIN
BEAUTIFUL BODIES
UNDER THE PROPER IDEOLOGY.
THE FIRST OF THESE NEW CITIZENS,
SOLDIERS WITH BEAUTIFUL BODIES
ARE NOW MARCHING
INTO THE NEW CITY.
THEY ARE THE SHAPES.
HARUHIKO, AT LONG LAST THE HILL
IS FINALLY COMING INTO VIEW.
- Man: MY PEOPLE, I ASK YOU
TO FOLLOW THEM.
MY PEOPLE, I ASK YOU
TO BELIEVE IN ME.
BELIEVE IN MY IDEALS,
BELIEVE IN MY VOICE,
BELIEVE IN THE FUTURE
OF THE NEW PEOPLE
AND THE NEW CITY.
BELIEVE IN THE MANIFESTATION
OF MY SPIRIT!
- Onishi: IT'S OVER.
IT SEEMS WE DON'T EVEN
HAVE TIME TO THINK.
- WE'LL DESTROY
EVERY ONE OF THEM!
- ( theme music playing )
- ( singing in Japanese )