- Man: IF THERE'S
ANYTHING YOU WANT,
ANYTHING AT ALL,
COME TO ME.
I'M YOUR GUARDIAN ANGEL.
- ( theme music playing )
- TEXHNOLYZED LIMBS
DEPEND ON THE OBELISK
FOR THEIR PRIMARY SOURCE
OF POWER
AND FOR ALL INFORMATION
RELATED TO THEIR MOVEMENTS.
- ( beeping )
- THEREFORE, THEY BECOME
USELESS ABOVE GROUND,
WHERE THERE IS NO OBELISK.
WHERE IS THE ONE FOR THE LEG?
HOWEVER, WITH THESE ATTACHED,
THEY ONLY CAN FUNCTION
TO A CERTAIN EXTENT
EVEN WHILE ABOVE GROUND.
SO?
YOU'LL ONLY HAVE ABOUT
60% OF YOUR NORMAL POWER.
AND THANK YOU.
YOU'VE BEEN MOST HELPFUL.
THE TRUTH IS THAT
I'M THE ONE INSIDE HERE.
THE BIOCIRCUIT I DESIGNED
ACTUALLY CONTAINS MY CELLS.
I'VE NEVER DONE THAT BEFORE.
I'M VERY SORRY I LIED TO YOU.
BUT IF I HADN'T,
I'M SURE YOU WOULD HAVE
TREATED THIS ARM CARELESSLY.
AFTER ALL, I HAD TO MAKE SURE
YOU WOULD TAKE GOOD CARE OF IT.
AT LEAST THIS ARM.
- ( brakes screeching )
- ( metal clanking )
- ( groaning )
( sighs )
- Man on radio:
SILENCE RECEDES.
I REPEAT,
I REPEAT, SILENCE RECEDES.
SILENCE RECEDES.
I REPEAT,
I REPEAT, SILENCE RECEDES.
( continues )
- WHERE ARE WE GOING?
- THE GOVERNMENT OFFICE.
- WILL WE BE ABLE TO WORK
SOMETHING OUT IF WE GO THERE?
- WELL...
( gasps )
- THEN YOU DON'T KNOW?
- I'M NOT TAKING THIS
WHOLE THING LIGHTLY.
IT'S JUST THAT'S
THE ONLY THING WE CAN DO.
HONESTLY.
- THERE'S NOT MUCH TIME.
- ( birds calling
from a distance )
- ( breathing heavily )
- DON'T EXERT YOURSELF TOO MUCH.
IF ANYTHING MALFUNCTIONS,
I'M NOT SURE I COULD
FIX IT HERE.
THAT GIRL WHO WAS STANDING
IN FRONT OF THE OBELISK...
THE SEER OF GABE--
SO WHAT IS SHE TO YOU?
SO WHERE IS EVERYBODY?
- TO BE HONEST,
I DON'T KNOW WHERE THEY ARE.
WHO KNOWS?
MAYBE THERE AREN'T
ANY HUMAN BEINGS
LEFT IN THIS PLACE ANYMORE.
- WHAT DO YOU MEAN BY THAT?
- YOU'LL UNDERSTAND SOON ENOUGH.
- ( breathing heavily )
- WE'RE ALMOST THERE.
AT LEAST I THINK.
- ( thunder rumbling )
- WHO'S THAT?
- HMM?
- Man's voice:
IT'S BEEN A WHILE, MR. SAKIMURA.
- UH, MR. SAGINUMA.
- Saginuma's voice:
SO, WHAT ARE YOU DOING?
- UH...
- YOU ONLY NEED TO ANSWER
TO THE BEST OF YOUR ABILITY.
- WELL, WE'RE GOING TO
THE GOVERNMENT OFFICE BUILDING.
- IS THAT YOUR
PRIMARY OBJECTIVE?
- UH, YEAH.
- THEN I'LL COME WITH YOU.
IF YOU DON'T MIND.
IF THAT IS YOUR OBJECTIVE,
MR. SAKIMURA.
WELL, SHALL WE GET GOING?
- HUH?
- NOW DO YOU SEE?
THERE AREN'T
ANY PEOPLE HERE ANYMORE
WHO ARE FULLY HUMAN.
- Man on radio: ONLY ONE GLASS
OF WATER BRIGHTENS THE WORLD.
- ( feedback )
- Man on radio: ONLY ONE GLASS
OF WATER BRIGHTENS THE WORLD.
ONLY ONE GLASS OF WATER
BRIGHTENS THE WORLD.
( continues )
- Saginuma's voice: HOW MUCH
DEMAND FOR TEXHNOLYZATION
IS THERE IN LUX?
- SORRY.
I'LL ANSWER ALL
YOUR ROUTINE QUESTIONS LATER.
WE RISKED OUR LIVES
TO GET UP HERE.
NOW THERE'S SOMETHING
WE HAVE TO TELL YOU.
IF YOU WOULD PLEASE
LET ME SPEAK.
- ROUTINE REMAINS ROUTINE
ONLY BECAUSE IT IS
CARRIED OUT AS ROUTINE.
THERE IS NO EXCEPTION
TO THE RULE.
- THIS IS OF THE UTMOST URGENCY!
- HOW MUCH DEMAND FOR
TEXHNOLYZATION IS THERE IN LUX?
ALSO, OF THE ENTIRE NUMBER
OF OPERATIONS PERFORMED IN LUX,
WHAT'S THE PERCENTAGE OF
OPERATIONS DONE BY YOU?
- ( deeply sighs )
- MR. SAKIMURA.
I'VE BEEN KEPT ON STANDBY
FOR QUITE SOME TIME NOW.
I DON'T HAVE MUCH TO DO.
AS YOU CAN SEE,
WE'VE KEPT YOUR DESK
EXACTLY AS YOU LEFT IT.
- BUT I JUST CAME BACK
FROM LUX TODAY.
- OH, I SEE.
- DO YOU REMEMBER YOSHII?
- OH, YES, YOSHII.
HOW IS HE DOING THESE DAYS?
- HE'S...
ACTUALLY, I KILLED HIM.
DO YOU UNDERSTAND?
I WAS THE ONE
WHO ACTUALLY MURDERED HIM.
( voice breaking )
I MURDERED HIM.
( sobbing )
- I'M SURE YOU DID
A FINE JOB OF IT.
- ( sobbing )
- Saginuma's voice:
COULD YOU TELL ME IF YOU HAVE
EVER KILLED ANYONE?
IF YOU HAVE KILLED ANYONE,
THEN HOW MANY?
- THEY'RE PLANNING TO ATTACK
THE SURFACE WORLD.
IF THEY DO, YOU WON'T REMAIN
UNAFFECTED ANYMORE.
- Saginuma's voice:
NO MATTER WHAT THEY DO,
IT WILL BE MEANINGLESS.
ALONG THE SAME LINE,
IT IS EQUALLY MEANINGLESS
FOR US TO DO ANYTHING TO THEM.
FOR ONE THING,
TEXHNOLYZED LIMBS
SHOULD BECOME
EITHER COMPLETELY
OR PARTIALLY INCAPACITATED.
BECAUSE THERE IS NO OBELISK
ABOVE GROUND,
WHICH ACTS AS
THEIR CONTROL SYSTEM.
JUST AS HE SHOULD BE.
- AREN'T YOU CONCERNED ABOUT
THE SUPPLY OF RAFFIA?
IT STOPPED.
- RAFFIA.
YES, I UNDERSTAND
WHY YOU WOULD THINK THAT.
BUT I'M SORRY TO SAY
THE REALITY IS
THAT WE NO LONGER
HAVE NEED OF IT.
OUR IMPORTING IT FROM LUX
HAS SIMPLY BECOME NOTHING MORE
THAN A FORMALITY NOW.
- WHAT ARE YOU SAYING?
- WE, THE SELECT FEW,
WHO ONLY CARRY
DOMINANT GENES,
WILL NEVER SUFFER
FROM BODILY DAMAGE.
EVEN IF WE DID, WE WOULDN'T TRY
TO DO ANYTHING ABOUT IT.
THE REALITY IS THAT RAFFIA
IS QUITE USELESS TO US.
WHAT GOOD IS IT TO
COMPENSATE FOR LOST LIMBS
BY REPLACING THEM
WITH ARTIFICIAL ONES?
WHAT ARE YOU GOING TO GRAB
WITH SUCH AN ARM?
AND WHAT ARE YOU GOING TO
STAND FIRMLY ON WITH SUCH A LEG?
I DON'T UNDERSTAND.
RAFFIA AND THE IDEA
OF TEXHNOLYZATION
ARE COMPLETELY ALIEN TO US.
MANKIND HAS GROWN OLD.
THE ONLY THING LEFT NOW IS
SLOW DEATH.
- Doc: MAYBE IT'S HARD
FOR ALL OF YOU TO UNDERSTAND,
SINCE YOU'RE JUST SITTING
AND WAITING FOR YOUR DEATHS,
BUT TEXHNOLYZATION
INFINITELY EXPANDS--
( sighs )
- Man on radio: A MIRROR
IMPROVES THE ABILITY TO THINK.
I REPEAT AGAIN,
A MIRROR IMPROVES
THE ABILITY TO THINK.
I REPEAT AGAIN,
A MIRROR IMPROVES
THE ABILITY TO THINK.
( continues )
- ( exhales )
- DO YOU WANNA REST?
THAT MAN OVER THERE...
- HUH?
WHAT IS IT?
- I DON'T KNOW,
BUT HE SOMEHOW
LOOKS FAMILIAR TO ME.
- ( slow melody playing )
- ( projector clatters, whirrs )
- ( theme music playing )
- ( singing in Japanese )