- Man: IF THERE'S
ANYTHING YOU WANT,
ANYTHING AT ALL,
COME TO ME.
I'M YOUR GUARDIAN ANGEL.
- ( theme music playing)
- Man: HOW LUX BECAME
THE CITY OF DOOM.
THE GIRL WAS FORCED
TO EXIST THERE
AS THE ONLY THING
THEY HAD TO PROTECT.
AN UNPRECEDENTED AMOUNT OF
BLOOD WAS SHED IN LUX.
THE KING OF
THIS WORLD STOOD BY
WATCHING THE BATTLE.
THE KING OF THIS WORLD
TOOK AWAY THE SANITY
FROM THE WORLD'S PEOPLE.
- Ran: KILL ME.
I'M THE ONE WHO DROVE
THIS CITY INSANE.
- VOICE OF THE CITY...
IT WAS YOU.
- YOU HAVE TO KILL ME.
I WANT YOU TO DO IT.
YOU, WHO HAS BEEN
LISTENING TO MY VOICE
ALL THESE YEARS.
YOU MUST KILL ME.
- IF THAT'S YOUR WISH.
- ( men chuckle )
- IF THE ONLY WAY TO BE
GRANTED LIFE IN THIS WORLD
IS TO SURRENDER MY BODY
AND SOUL TO INSANITY,
THEN I SHALL CHOOSE
TO MEET MY DOOM!
( shouts )
- ONISHI!
- Onishi: DIE!
- ( gasping )
( shouts )
- IT'S HIM.
- WHO?
- THE ONE WHO GOT
INTO THE ORGANO.
LET'S TEAR HIM APART TOO.
- ( breathing heavily )
- Ichise: RAN.
SAY SOMETHING.
I'M GONNA HAVE TO
DO IT AGAIN.
- ( gasps )
- ( grunts )
( shouts )
- ( grunting )
- ( stammers )
YOU RABID DOG!
- ( grunts )
Ichise: YOU ARE...
SUPPOSED TO BE MY ARM.
YOU ARE...
SUPPOSED TO BE MY LEG.
MOVE.
( gasps )
MY ARM.
MY LEG.
- ( men gasp )
- ( chuckles )
WHAT IS IT?
- ( gasps )
- ( grunts )
DOC.
( panting )
- Kohakura: OH, YOU.
YOU'RE ONE OF ONISHI'S.
HEY.
YOU'RE STILL ABLE TO MOVE.
- Ichise: IF YOU WANT
TO DIE, JUST TELL ME.
- DIE?
WHAT ARE YOU TALKING ABOUT?
YOU MUST UNDERSTAND,
THE REASON WE WERE REBORN
WAS TO HAVE THESE BODIES,
AND TO LIVE NEAR
ETERNAL LIVES.
I CAME TO UNDERSTAND
THAT TEXHNOLYZATION
IS A MEANS OF REFORMING
THE HUMAN SPECIES,
WHICH HAS COME
TO A DEAD END.
IT WAS MEANT TO ENHANCE US.
WE'VE BEEN FORTUNATE
TO LIVE A LIFE
THAT TAKES ROOT ON EARTH.
AND THUS MAINTAINS
OUR ABILITY TO THINK
FOR A LONG TIME.
IS ONISHI STILL ALIVE?
THERE'S ONE THING
I REGRET.
I REGRET NOT ADVISING HIM
MORE STRONGLY THAT
HE SHOULD HAVE OBEYED
THE WORDS OF MASTER KANO.
- ( beeps )
- THAT'S FINE.
TAKE IT.
SOMEONE TOLD ME LONG AGO
WHAT THIS PLACE IS.
WHAT HE SAID
MAKES PERFECT SENSE.
HE CALLED IT
THE NINTH ANNEX
OF THE REVIVING HELL.
- THE ONLY THING LEFT
IS FOR US TO WATCH, THEORIA.
WHY COULDN'T YOU JUST
REMAIN BEING MY DEAR SISTER?
- HEY.
I'VE CHANGED,
ISN'T THAT RIGHT?
NOT BECAUSE
I GOT THIS ARM,
BECAUSE I MET YOU.
I'M STILL DOING...
THE SAME OLD THING.
BUT WHAT I'M ABOUT
TO DO NOW
IS WHAT I'VE BEEN
DOING ALL MY LIFE
JUST TO SURVIVE.
DOES THAT MEAN
WHATEVER I DO
DOESN'T CHANGE THINGS
NO MATTER WHAT?
THAT'S NOT TRUE,
IS IT?
HAVE YOU CHANGED AT ALL
BECAUSE YOU MET ME?
- Kano: SO IT WAS YOU
WHOM THEORIA WAS WATCHING.
- TELL ME WHERE IS RAN?
- THEORIA WILL NEVER AGAIN
VOICE WHAT SHE SEES.
- Ichise:
WHY DID YOU DO ALL THIS?
I THOUGHT YOU WERE
GOING TO THE SURFACE
WITH YOUR SOLDIERS IN TOW.
- IT WAS MEANINGLESS
FROM THE BEGINNING.
I WAS WELL AWARE
THAT THE WORLD ABOVE
WAS ABOUT TO DIE OUT.
I WANTED TO SEE FOR CERTAIN
HOW MUCH TEXHNOLYZATION
COULD CHANGE
A HUMAN BEING'S
CONSCIOUSNESS.
AND SO REVENGE
WAS THE IDEAL WAY TO MOTIVATE
THE PEOPLE OF THIS PLACE.
BESIDES,
WE WEREN'T FORCED
TO COME HERE.
THE HUMAN SPECIES
THAT'S ABOUT TO COME
TO THE END OF ITS LIFE
WAS BORN HERE.
AND IT HAS COME
FULL CIRCLE.
- TELL ME WHERE IS RAN.
- HAVING EXPANDED MY MIND
BY TEXHNOLYZATION,
I CAME TO UNDERSTAND
THAT LUX IS INSIDE MY MIND.
IT'S A DELUSION
THAT WE HAVE GENES
THAT NO HUMAN BEING
SHOULD HAVE.
I BECAME FREE
OF ALL GENES
BY HAVING INTERCOURSE
WITH LUX.
WE MUST NOW ENDURE
A LONG PASSAGE OF TIME
IN ORDER TO BECOME
A DIFFERENT LIFE FORM.
THEY RECEIVED THEIR BODIES
IN PREPARATION FOR THAT.
I'M SANER THAN
ANYONE ELSE.
MY DEAR SISTER,
THEORIA,
KNOWS IT BETTER
THAN ANYONE.
BUT SADLY,
THEORIA WON'T SPEAK AGAIN.
UNFORTUNATELY,
SHE KILLED HER OWN MIND.
- ( gasps )
- Kano: SHE CAN'T BE
MY EYES ANYMORE.
- ( breathing deep )
- WHAT IS IT THAT
YOU'RE AFRAID OF?
TO KILL ME,
WHO IS SANER THAN ANYONE,
IS TO ACKNOWLEDGE
YOUR OWN INSANITY,
AND TO EMBRACE IT
UNTIL YOU DIE.
- ♪ I DIP MY HANDS ♪
♪ INTO THIS DARKNESS ♪
♪ THIS IS THE INK ♪
♪ OF OUR LIFETIMES ♪
♪ HERE IN THIS WORLD
OF UTTER SILENCE ♪
♪ LET THE STONES
SPEAK TO ME ♪
♪ TATTOOED HERE
ACROSS MY SKIN ♪
♪ "I WILL LIVE" ♪
♪ LIKE A ROSE ♪
♪ THAT GROWS FROM
THE WRECKAGE ♪
♪ BLOOD RED ♪
♪ BEAUTIFUL ♪
♪ HOW THE STORMS
ALL AROUND ME ARE NOW ♪
♪ BREATHLESS ♪
♪ IS THIS THE END
OF THE RAGING ROAD ♪
♪ THROUGH THE TANGLED MIND? ♪
♪ IS THIS THE END
OF STARLIT SKY? ♪
♪ ARE WE WALKING BLIND? ♪
♪ LET ME SAIL OUT
THROUGH THIS MORNING ♪
♪ OPEN ARMS ♪
♪ TO GREET THE EMPTY AGES ♪
♪ REBORN ♪
♪ SEE HOW I'M CIRCLING ♪
♪ I'M A SAILOR ♪
♪ ETERNAL ♪
♪ IS THIS THE END ♪
♪ OF THE WASTED WAY? ♪
♪ IS THIS THE DEATH OF TIME? ♪
♪ IT IS THE END ♪
♪ OF BLUE PSYCHIC SEAS? ♪
♪ ARE WE SAILING BLIND? ♪
♪ OH, LOOK DOWN ON ME ♪
♪ WATCH OVER ME ♪
♪ AS I WALK ACROSS
THIS WORLD ♪
♪ OH, HOLD ME ♪
♪ IN HIDDEN HANDS ♪
♪ LET US GO ♪
♪ OH, LOOK DOWN ON ME ♪
♪ WATCH OVER ME ♪
♪ AS I WALK ACROSS
THIS WORLD ♪
♪ TEACH ME HOW TO TAKE ♪
♪ MY FIRST FOOTSTEPS ♪
♪ TO THE END. ♪