- Man: IF THERE'S
ANYTHING YOU WANT,
ANYTHING AT ALL,
COME TO ME.
I'M YOUR GUARDIAN ANGEL.
- ( theme music playing )
- Man: UNFORTUNATELY, THE AMOUNT
OF RAFFIA BEING DUG UP
IS IN FACT DIMINISHING.
THEY'RE AREN'T A LOT OF SPOTS
LEFT WHERE WE CAN DIG, EITHER.
- ( bell rings )
- WELL, YES, OF COURSE.
I DO UNDERSTAND.
WHAT?  WHAT SUSPICION?
WHAT DO YOU MEAN?
WELL, BECAUSE I JUST WANNA KNOW.
THAT'S ALL.
THAT'S VERY TRUE.
IF THEY'RE GONNA MAKE
RIDICULOUS ACCUSATIONS,
WE'LL GO TO THE ORGANO.
- ( crashing )
- HMM?
HMM?  OH!
- ( gunshots )
- All: HUH?
- Man: YOU THINK YOU
CAN MESS WITH ME?
THIS AREA IS GONNA BE MADE
INTO THE RACAN'S TERRITORY.
I KNOW YOU DON'T LIKE PAYING
A LOT OF MONEY, DO YOU, GRANDMA?
AND TO BE PERFECTLY HONEST,
WE'RE JUST THE SAME
AS YOU PEOPLE.
WE'RE NOT HERE TO ROB YOU.
IT'S AGAINST MY BETTER NATURE
TO WRING A LOT
OF MONEY OUT OF YOU.
HMM?  HUH?
WE'RE HERE TO PROTECT YOU,
YOU KNOW?
YOU WANNA COME WITH ME?
I'LL SHOW YOU A GOOD TIME.
HUH?
WHAT?
WHAT THE HELL ARE YOU?
HA!  LOSERS FROM GABE.
WHY DON'T YOU JUST GO BACK
TO THE MOUNTAIN AND SQUIRM
AROUND IN SOME PIG GREASE?
HUH?  ( grunts )
YOU BASTARDS WILL NEVER
GET AWAY WITH THIS.
- HEY!
- Toyama: TELL ME.
DO YOU HAVE CONFIDENCE
IN YOUR BODY?
WITH THAT NEW ARM,
YOU THINK YOU HAVE NO NEED
FOR ANY OTHER WEAPON?
- WEAPON?
- A SWORD IS JUST AN OUTDATED
WEAPON THE PEOPLE OF GABE USED
IN THE OLD DAYS.
GUNS ARE MORE POPULAR THESE DAYS
'CAUSE THEY'RE SIMPLER.
- WHY ARE YOU TELLING ME
ANY OF THIS?
- YOU ARE NO LONGER
A GAME PLAYER.
IN LUX, USING AXES AND GUNS TO
FIGHT IS THE WAY OF THE LOWLIFE.
- BUT I HAVEN'T CHANGED
FROM BEFORE.
- PROBABLY NOT.
BUT YOU ARE NOW A MEMBER
OF THE ORGANO.
AND YOU MUST LEARN
THAT A MEMBER MUST ALWAYS SHOW
ABSOLUTE STRENGTH
TOWARDS NON-MEMBERS.
- WHAT A PAIN.
- YES, IT'S QUITE A PAIN.
YES, YOU MUST MAKE THE SWORD
AN EXTENSION OF YOUR FINGERS.
- LIKE I SAID, WE SHOULD GO
SET UP OUR DEN OVER THERE,
AND THEN WE SHOULD BEAT UP
WHOEVER DISOBEYS US.
THAT'LL TEACH 'EM A LESSON,
YOU KNOW?
AND ONE MORE THING,
LET ME BE IN CHARGE
OF SOME OF OUR SOLDIERS.
COME ON.
- IT'S ABOUT TIME YOU STOPPED
ACTING LIKE A SPOILED BRAT.
- OKAY, OKAY, OKAY.
( grunts )
- HMM?
HEY, SO WHERE THE HELL
HAVE YOU BEEN?
WE REALLY GOTTA DECIDE QUICKLY
ON THE LOCATION OF OUR NEW DEN.
- YEAH.
- SHINJI, I DIDN'T KNOW
YOU WERE HERE.
- HAL, WHAT DO YOU THINK OF OUR
CAPABILITIES TO FIGHT A WAR?
- WELL, TO BE COMPLETELY HONEST,
IF WE MAKE A BUNCH OF FOOLS
OF OURSELVES AGAIN
IN ANOTHER SPECTACLE,
THE GUYS BELOW US WILL--
HEY, YOKO.
WHY DON'T YOU GO
GET US SOME DRINKS?
AND WHILE YOU'RE AT IT,
GET US SOMETHING TO EAT TO.
- SURE, AFTER MY HAIR DRIES.
- JUST GO.
- ALL RIGHT THEN.
SHINJI, SO WHAT DO YOU WANT?
- WHATEVER'S FINE.
- ( scoffs )
YOU TWO ARE SO PATHETIC.
YOU HAVE NOTHING BETTER
TO DO THAN CHAT THE DAY AWAY.
- Toyama: THE MANAGER
OF THE DIG SITE WAS KILLED.
- RIGHT.
BUT THANKS TO MIZUNO'S
BLUNDERED POWER GRAB,
THE MANAGEMENT HAS GONE HAYWIRE.
APPARENTLY, THEY KILLED
THE ASSASSIN,
AN EXPENDABLE UNDERLING
NO DOUBT,
WITHOUT EXTRACTING INFORMATION
FROM HIM.
- Toyama:
COULD IT BE THE UNION?
- IF IT IS, THEN WE
HAVE A SERIOUS PROBLEM.
- ALL RIGHT,
I'LL LOOK INTO IT.
- WHY DON'T YOU GO ALONG
WITH TOYAMA?
- WHY DID THE CHIEF
LET HER COME HERE
ALL BY HERSELF?
- I DON'T KNOW.
MAYBE SHE'S TAKING A FIELD TRIP.
- ( laughing )
- IT'S NOT FUNNY. IF SOMETHING
EVER HAPPENS TO HER,
THERE'S NO WAY WE'LL BE ABLE
TO DEAL WITH IT ON OUR OWN.
- THE ORGANO GUYS
WON'T TOUCH HER.
BUT WHO KNOWS ABOUT ANYBODY ELSE
WHO DOESN'T KNOW WHO SHE IS?
- THOSE WHO DO KNOW
ARE MORE DANGEROUS.
( sighs )
I DON'T KNOW.
MAYBE WE SHOULD REPORT
THIS BACK TO THE MOUNTAIN.
- HMM.  HUH?
- Man:
YOU'VE GROWN SO MUCH.
I KNOW YOU.
YOU'RE IKUSEI'S SON.
YOU'RE TALLER, BUT THERE'S
A STRIKING RESEMBLANCE.
HOW ARE YOU?  IT'S BEEN A VERY
LONG TIME SINCE I LAST SAW YOU.
HOW'S YOUR MOTHER DOING?
I SEE.
- MY FATHER--
NO, NEVER MIND.
I ALREADY KNOW.
- YOU KNOW YOUR FATHER WAS--
- BEING PAID FOR SELLING OUT
HIS OWN PEOPLE, WASN'T HE?
- THAT'S NO WAY TO TALK
ABOUT YOUR FATHER.
- SOLD OUT HIS OWN PEOPLE
AND DIED MISERABLY.
THE BASTARD LOST EVERYTHING
AND HAD ONLY HIMSELF TO BLAME.
- Ran: I CAN SEE
EVERYTHING.
BUT--
- Toyama: WE THE PEOPLE OF THE
LUX ARE KEPT ALIVE BY THE CLASS
IN ORDER TO COLLECT RAFFIA.
DO YOU THINK THE PEOPLE ABOVE
NEED RAFFIA SO BADLY?
- THAT'S NONE OF MY BUSINESS.
- YOU HAVE HEARD WHY
THIS IS THE ONLY PLACE
THAT PRODUCES RAFFIA,
HAVE YOU NOT?
THAT IN THE OLD DAYS,
A COUNTLESS NUMBER
OF BODIES WERE BURIED HERE.
- NO, I NEVER HEARD THAT.
- I BELIEVE YOUR FATHER
WAS A WATCHMAN HERE, WAS HE NOT?
FATHERS ARE JUST STRANGERS
THAT HAPPEN TO BE RELATED
TO YOU BY BLOOD.
- ( chiming )
- THERE'S SOMETHING FISHY
ABOUT THE MURDERED MANAGER.
APPARENTLY HE OFTEN WENT OUT
TO MEET WITH SOMEONE.
- WHAT'LL WE DO?
- WE HAVE TO FIND OUT
WHO HE WAS MEETING WITH.
- Man: THAT LADY DOCTOR
FROM THE CLASS IS TAKING CARE
OF THOSE LEGS OF YOURS, RIGHT?
- Onishi:
WHAT ARE YOU TRYING TO SAY?
- DON'T YOU WANNA SEE
WHAT IT'S LIKE UP ON THE HILL?
I'M THINKING MAYBE WE'RE
WASTING TIME WORRYING
AND FIGHTING ABOUT LITTLE PIECES
OF TERRITORY.
WHAT I'M TRYING TO SAY IS
I DON'T WANNA GROW OLD
IN THE SAME WAY
AS THOSE OLD BASTARDS DID.
- DON'T YOU THINK IT WOULD BE
WISE TO REFRAIN FROM MAKING
SUCH DANGEROUS REMARKS?
- LOOKING BACK AT THAT
PYROMANIAC FROM THE SURFACE,
I'M BEGINNING TO THINK
HIS IDEA ITSELF WASN'T SO BAD.
- SO WHAT ARE YOU TRYING TO SAY?
WHAT DO YOU WANT FROM ME?
- NOTHING.
I DON'T EXPECT TO GET ANYTHING
FROM YOU FOR THE MOMENT.
HOWEVER,
IT WOULDN'T HURT TO KNOW
WHAT I CAN GET.
- LIKE DOC.
SHE'S JUST A WOMAN WHO ABANDONED
THE CLASS TO COME HERE.
- YES, THAT'S THE KIND OF THING
I WANT TO KNOW.
I'LL HAVE YOUR OFFICE READY
FOR YOU VERY SHORTLY.
- THE MURDERED MAN WAS
APPARENTLY ILLEGALLY SELLING
PART OF HIS SHIPMENT
OF RAFFIA.
- THAT HURTS.
- TELL ME.
WHY ARE YOU AVOIDING ME?
- BECAUSE I DON'T WANNA SEE IT.
- SEE WHAT?
- YOUR FUTURE.
I DON'T WANT THE FUTURE
THAT I SOUGHT FOR YOU
TO COME TRUE.
- MY WHAT?  TELL ME.
WHAT DID YOU SEE?
PLEASE TELL ME,
WHAT DID YOU SEE ABOUT ME?
IT'S MY FUTURE.
I WANNA KNOW ABOUT IT.
- ICHISE.
- ( gasps )
- ( Ran screaming )
- HELP.  SOMEONE.
- Man:
BRING HER OVER HERE.
SHE JUST GOT A LITTLE UPSET.
THAT'S ALL.
- RAN.
SHE SAID THAT SHE'D
SEEN MY FUTURE.
- THAT'S BECAUSE
SHE'S A SEER.
THERE'S SOMETHING I WANT
TO TELL YOU.
I SEE YOU'VE BEEN RESENTING
YOUR FATHER ALL THIS TIME.
THAT'S UNDERSTANDABLE.
BUT YOU'RE NOT BEING
FAIR TO HIM.
IKUSEI DIDN'T BETRAY
HIS PEOPLE.
OTHERS CAME TO HOLD GRUDGES
AGAINST HIM
BECAUSE HE WAS TRYING
TO PREVENT US DIGGERS
FROM SELLING RAFFIA
THROUGH ILLEGAL CHANNELS.
IF ANYONE DID THAT,
IT WOULD BE A SERIOUS CRIME.
AND THAT PERSON
WOULD HAVE TO BE PUNISHED.
THAT'S WHY IKUSEI KEPT
HIS MOUTH SHUT.
KEPT IT SHUT AND DIED QUIETLY.
- NOW TELL ME WHO FRAMED
MY FATHER.
- WHAT GOOD DOES IT DO
FOR YOU TO KNOW NOW?
- ( grunting )
WHAT?
WHAT ARE YOU TRYING TO SHOW ME?
TELL ME.
- IS EVERYTHING ALL RIGHT
WITH YOU?
- MY MOTHER KNEW.
- THINGS ARE VERY DIFFERENT
RIGHT NOW.
YOU SHOULDN'T GET IDEAS
ABOUT SETTLING OLD SCORES.
- AND WHAT ARE YOU TRYING
TO SAY TO ME?
- Onishi: WELL, I DO NOT
THINK THERE'S ANY NEED
FOR YOU TO BE ALARMED
AT THIS POINT.
HOWEVER, THERE'S NO HARM
IN BEING TOO CAUTIOUS.
- IT'S NOT A BAD THING
TO HAVE AMBITION.
IN FACT, I'D SAY IT'S
RATHER NECESSARY HERE IN LUX,
BUT HAVING AMBITION WITHOUT
REGARD FOR ONE'S POSITION
WOULD ONLY HURT ONESELF.
- I BELIEVE I AM
WELL AWARE OF THAT, DOC.
- OH, THAT'S GOOD TO HEAR.
I'M SIMPLY SAYING THAT
BECAUSE I'M DEEPLY CONCERNED
ABOUT HOW YOU'RE ADJUSTING
TO YOUR LEGS.
- AT ANY RATE,
I'M MERELY OFFERING YOU
THIS PIECE OF ADVICE.
THE ORGANO IS NOT MONOLITHIC.
GOODBYE.
- IT'S TIME
FOR THE EXECUTIVE MEETING.
PARDON ME FOR SAYING,
BUT I THINK YOU NEED SOME REST.
PERHAPS IN MY APARTMENT.
- THERE'S NO NEED FOR CONCERN.
- Toyama: I THOUGHT IT WAS
THE UNION WHO APPROACHED HIM
WITH THE IDEA OF SELLING
RAFFIA ILLEGALLY.
BUT IT DOESN'T SEEM
TO BE THE CASE.
AND OF COURSE, IT WASN'T
THE RACAN, EITHER.
IT SEEMS MY WAY OF THINKING
IS TOO OLD-FASHIONED.
I THOUGHT IN ORDER
TO GAIN POWER,
ONE MUST BE
AMONG THE POWERFUL.
BUT MAYBE THAT'S JUST
AN OBSOLETE IDEA.
DO YOU MISS IT HERE?
- ( shouting )
- ( cheering )
- GET 'EM!  GET 'EM!
GET 'EM!  GET 'EM!
- IT'S YOU.
- DO YOU HAVE BUSINESS
WITH HIM?
- NO, NOT AT ALL.  SORRY.
- WE HEARD THERE WAS A MAN
WHO RECENTLY SPENT A GOOD DEAL
OF MONEY DOWN HERE.
- ( laughing )
EVERYBODY WHO COMES HERE ALWAYS
SPENDS A GOOD DEAL OF MONEY.
- IS THAT THE ANSWER
YOU WISH TO GIVE ME?
- I DIDN'T MEAN IT LIKE THAT,
SIR.
PERHAPS THOSE GUYS BACK THERE.
THEY SEEM TO BE BETTING A LOT
MORE THESE DAYS.
- I SEE.
- ( laughing )
- YOU SEEM TO BE DOING
QUITE WELL.
TELL ME.  HOW CAN YOU AFFORD
TO SPEND SO MUCH?
- WHO THE HELL ARE YOU?
- WE JUST SAVED, RIGHT?
USING JUST WHAT WE MANAGED
TO SCRAPE FROM OUR WAGES.
HEY, RELAX, HAVE A DRINK.
- ( cheering )
- HUH?
- ( gasps )
- YOU'RE THE ONE WHO
FRAMED MY FATHER.
- ( growls )
- ( crowd cheering )
- ( panting )
- ( theme music playing )
- ( singing in Japanese )