[harp music]
[gulls calling]
[flute music]
[music continues]
[whizzing]
[whizzing continues]
[sighs]
Huh?
[gentle music]
Poor innocent creature.
As the Westwind, the gods have
ordered me to abandon you
on the hill of oblivion,
but I cannot do it.
Instead I will leave you
here, Unico
and pray that the gods
don't find you.
Once again you are all alone.
You will remember nothing
of what has happened.
Goodbye Unico.
[echo]
[click]
Where am I?
How did I get here?
Is anybody here?
There's got to be somebody.
[shouts] Hey!
Can anybody hear me--
[Melvin shouts] Hey! Put a lid
on it! I'm trying to sleep.
Yippee, there's somebody here!
There's somebody here.
[giggling]
[electronic pops]
Hey! Where are you? [gasps]
Hehe, oh, there you are.
Who are you?
What do you mean, who am I?
Where have you been?
Mars or something?
I am Melvin Manificat,
and this is my forest.
Oh, Melvin Manificat.
That certainly is
an attractive coat you have.
[grunts] You better believe it.
It strikes terror
into the hearts
of anyone that sees it.
Ow! [groans]
Oh, are you alright?
Oh, shut up!
[Melvin] Where you from Peewee?
[Unico] I don't know.
Where you headed?
I don't know.
I never met anybody before
who didn't know where
he came from,
or where he's headed to.
Lots of luck, Peewee.
[gasps]
What in the world are you?
I'm Unico.
Well, what sort
of a name is that?
What sort of a thing are you?
I'm Unico, that's all,
just Unico.
Yeah, yeah, but what
exactly is a unico? [sobbing]
Maybe you're some kind of sheep?
[sighs]
Oh.
[Unico] No, I don't think
I'm any kind of sheep.
Ooh, well, I ain't never seen
nothing like you before.
I don't like your looks.
Oh wait, what are you doing?
-I'm Unico, that's all I know.
-[screams] Stay away from me!
-Get back!
-I'm not going to do anything.
That's what you say.
What's that horn
doing on your head?
Oh, oh, oh.
[electronic squeak]
You're just waiting to stick me
with it as soon as my back
-is turned.
I wouldn't do anything
-like that--
-Yeah! Stay away from me. Oh!
[gasping] Go ahead, kill me,
I'm all yours, get it over with.
[sobs] I'm so young.
I have my whole life
ahead of me.
-[sobbing continues]
-Now then,
-Huh?
-Take a good look at that guy
-you're so scared of.
-What?
You know, when you start falling
like a baby in front of a midget
like that, we begin to wonder
whether you should be the boss
of this forest anymore.
[stutters] But his horn?
Eh, it's the size
of a toothpick,
it couldn't harm a flea.
[gasps] Oh-uh.
Watch out! [groans]
-What's the big idea?
-Hm?
Thought you could pull
a fast one on me, did ya?
-Hm? Mm.
-[gasping] Oh, oh.
Ha-ha, you're not so tough
after all, are you?
I'll teach you to make a fool
outta Melvin Manificat.
-[gasps] Ow, ow.
-[screams] I'm gonna kill you!
I'm gonna turn that horn
of yours into mandolin picks.
Stop right where you are Peewee!
-I won't.
-[screaming continues]
Okay, that does it,
now you made me mad.
-[chuckles]
-There he goes.
[gasps and screams]
If he knows what's good for him,
he'll clear out of my forest,
-and pronto. Come on.
-You handled that real good.
Well, that's what a boss
is for after all.
Yeah, that's true enough.
[gentle music]
[electronic pop]
[groans]
He told me to get
out of his forest.
But I don't' know
which way is out.
Hm?
[lightening]
Hi, I'm Unico, who are you?
[sighs]
Huh?
Hi, I'm Unico.
Oh, nobody seems to
like me in this forest.
[flute music]
Huh?
[music continues]
[wind howling]
[flute crescendo]
[squeaks]
[music continues]
-[Melvin growling]
-Huh?
-[gasps]
-[growls] What's that guy
thinking he's trying to muscle
his way into my territory.
-[growls]
-It's kinda nice music, ya know.
It almost makes you
wanna cry, don't it? [gasps]
[shouts] Hey you! That's it,
the party's over, knock it off.
-[squeaks]
-That's better, now take that
little flute of yours
and fly away.
Get outta here!
Hey! Did you hear me?
[electronic swish]
Huh?
Who is that guy?
Hey! Put an egg in your shoe
and beat it, you heard the boss,
get lost!
[electronic crescendo]
[electronic swiping]
[all groan]
Huh? What's going on?
[screams]
Hey, what's the--
[electronic beep]
[gasps]
Oh no.
What's going on, huh?
What's going on?
Listen, I [stutters]--
[electronic swoop]
[Melvin] Whoa!
You, you just better watch
your step around here.
I can't believe this
is happening to me.
[gasps] Wait just a minute,
you stay away!
This is your last warning! No!
No, no not so fast,
Listen to me, stop, will ya.
[sobs]
Parle vous Franscais?
Spreken ze Deutch?
Stop! Whoa!
[electronic swipes]
[thud]
[swiping continues]]
[electronic trembling]
[rings]
[swish]
[electronic swish]
[Melvin panting]
[yelps]
[panting continues]
[screams] No!
[swishing continues]
[stuttered gasps]
Stop it! Don't hurt me please,
I beg of ya. [sobs]
[panting] Ha-ha,
I know what, I'll
give you this free of charge,
if you let me go,
what do you say, huh?
Yeah! Wait, wait a minute,
at least let me explain to ya.
What you got here is your
most advanced stereophonic
sound system in the world.
In this box,
you got your tweeter,
and here's your woofer see?
First the tweeter,
[singing]
then the woofer.
[low croaks]
Ain't that the cat's pajamas,
hm-mm?
When you put 'em on,
you just can't stop your feet
from dancing, you see?
[sings beats]
I tell ya, it's the living end,
and I'll give it to you
as a present if you only
promise not to zap me, huh?
No wait! Okay, okay,
that was a stupid idea,
but listen, I'll serve you,
I'll be your slave,
I'll do anything you say,
really I will, really.
Perhaps you could
be of use to me.
He he, sure, sure, he he.
So be it, you shall serve me.
[electronic zap]
I must turn all the animals
of the forest
into living puppets.
What do you mean puppets?
Just that. I turn them
into living puppets.
But why would you want
to do something like that, huh?
That's no concern of yours.
Your job is to help me
locate the animals.
Okay, okay,
it's your party, pal.
Let's see, what have
we got here?
Oh, look over there, a squirrel.
[loud zap]
[gasps]
[zappings]
They're quick, aren't they?
[grunts] A couple of rabbits
over there.
Hmm.
These creatures are too small.
You must find me
something bigger.
It would help if you could
shoot straight. [gasps]
[chuckles] I got ya.
Back there, just what
you're looking for, ha.
Whoa!
[groaning]
-Mm, what's this, I've never
-[screams]
-seen anything like it.
-[gasps]
And what sort of animal are you?
Come on, come on,
turn him into a puppet.
This I gotta see.
-[screaming]
-I think the master will be
pleased with this one.
-Whoa!
-[screaming continues]
[zapping]
There he goes, there.
Quick, shoot him, shoot him!
Come on.
Whoa! Whoa! Watch out,
watch out, watch out!
-Be quiet.
-[muffled screams]
I told you to watch out.
-Why didn't you listen to me?
-Oh, shut up!
That's just great.
I tried to save your neck
and you tell me to shut up.
I don't like this relationship.
-Listen, you little--
-Okay, okay.
[running water]
[gentle music]
[music continues]
-[Melvin] Er, say boss?
-You may call me Toby.
-Toby?
-That is my name.
Well, Toby, once the animals
have been turned into living
puppets, what's next?
That is not for you to know.
Ah, come on, I'm your pal,
you can tell me.
-Can't you give me a hint?
-Shh.
Be quiet, you fool,
the master is approaching.
[Karuku] Toby.
Toby.
[yells] Toby.
-[trembling]
-I'm here, Lord Karuku.
Your wish is my command.
I hope you have not
been lazy, Toby.
No Master.
Is the ship ready for departure?
Yes Master.
And its cargo of living puppets?
Are they ready as well?
[stutters] It has proven more
difficult to catch the animals
than I had hoped, Master.
[scoffs] I am not
interested in excuses, Toby.
I'm sorry, Lord Karuku.
Well, you will just have
to work harder, won't you?
Because I simply have to have
my living puppets, don't I?
-Yes Master.
-Oh yes, Toby,
once you're finished
with all the animals,
you may begin collecting... people.
Collecting people?
I believe that's what I said.
They are such stupid things,
that I am sure they'll be even
easier for you to deal with
than the animals.
You may begin with those houses
down in the valley there.
You'd do that for me, won't you?
-Toby?
-I will of course, Master.
And in return you will teach
me more of your magic?
Hurry up and bring the living
puppets to my island.
And if I am pleased, I suppose
I might teach you another
-magic trick.
-[Toby] Master.
And be quick about it too, Toby.
Yes, Lord Karuku.
[electronic whizzing]
[stuttering] What was that?
A magician.
And my master.
That's some trick appearing
and disappearing like that.
Did he say he wanted
you to start turning people
into living puppets? Ha,
that's my idea of a good time.
I never liked people,
can't stand 'em, come on,
zap 'em. Oh boy, I can't
wait to see this, ha.
Be quiet, unless you want
to be the very first to undergo
-the transformation.
-[trembling sighs]
This wasn't part of the bargain.
[Melvin] Say, are you really
gonna zap every one
of the people down there?
Every one? [cries]
-I said be quiet.
-Sorry.
[Sherry] Huh, he's awake.
It's amazing he's still alive
after all that he's
been through.
[giggles] Isn't he cute?
Are you alright? Huh?
It looks like somebody
ruffed the little fellow up.
Here you go, drink some milk.
[father] I can't say I've ever
seen anything quite like him.
Here, you gotta have
some of this milk.
That way you'll get
your strength back.
Come on.
Here, watch me and I'll show
you how to do it, alright?
[scoffs] He's probably
frightened of people.
Well, I'll take care of that.
You see that man at the table
smoking a pipe?
That man is my father.
And that woman with her hands
in the suds is my mother.
Is it working?
[sighs] There you go.
There used to be another
person here, my older brother.
But he went away.
That was almost
three years ago now.
I wonder where he is,
what he's doing.
It's time we forgot about him.
Enough! I'm certain he's
forgotten all about us by now.
I have an early day,
I'm turning in.
-Goodnight, Father.
-[sighs]
[Mother] Goodnight.
Why do I make Father angry
whenever I mention my brother?
Your father's not angry
with you, dear.
When a man is worried
by something inside him,
and he's too proud
to weep or cry out,
he sometimes gets angry
at those around him.
But he's not angry with you,
not with you.
Poor little fellow, you look
like you haven't a friend
in the world.
Me too.
I lost my best friend
when I lost my brother.
Don't be frightened.
From now on, we can be
each other's best friend.
Isn't that right, Mother?
[Mother] That's right, Sherry.
So, let's have
a little milk now.
Come on, what's wrong with you?
You've got to drink some.
Sherry, don't threaten him,
you're just frightening him
all the more.
[giggles] Sorry.
He'll be better in the morning.
Come along, it's time for bed.
-Mother?
-Yes Dear?
May I stay up with him
a little longer?
-Alright, don't be too long.
-I won't. Goodnight.
I like you, you know.
I like all animals.
Birds and rabbits,
and squirrels and everything.
And I like... my brother.
I like him a lot.
I'm... Unico.
[birds tweeting]
[Sherry] I like all animals.
Birds and rabbits,
and everything.
And I like you too.
[sighs]
[gentle sigh]
[gasps] So you're not afraid
of me anymore, are you?
-I'm Unico.
-[gasps] Unico?
[Sherry yells] Mother? Father?
The little one is all better.
Come on, I'll race
you to the bridge.
-Faster, Unico. Faster. [laughs]
-[giggling]
Come on!
Here, we're friends now, we
must swear eternal friendship,
so no matter what happens
we'll stand by each other.
Let's shake hands.
-Come on!
-Okay.
-[Unico giggling] Wait for me.
-Come on.
-[Unico] Where are you?
-I'm over here.
There you are.
[thunder]
Sherry? Come on
into the house now.
It looks like it's
going to rain.
Come on now.
[lightening cracks]
[trembling]
Don't worry, there's nothing
to be frightened of.
I thought you were
a brave little fella.
Just repeat, \"I'm not scared,\"
three times and you'll be fine.
[loud gasp] I guess
it is a little scary.
-Hm?
-Huh?
[creaking]
[wind howls]
Ja, ja. [laughs]
What is it you want?
It's my big brother,
he's come home.
-[stutters] Toby, is that you?
-Oh, yes, it is you!
You've come home at last.
[Sherry] So where have
you been all this time?
-We were so worried about you.
-[Mother] Oh, Toby.
But my boy, what on earth
is that you've got on?
It looks like
a magician's costume, Toby?
That's exactly
what it is, Mother.
Hm?
[electronic beeps]
-[gasps]
-Huh?
Oh no, that terrible man
is Sherry's lost brother.
[sniffing]
[fire crackling]
This smells kind of familiar.
Hm.
[Toby] Sherry,
I've brought you a gift.
[sniffing continues]
Hm.
-Hm, hm.
-Oh.
Watch closely now.
Isn't it the loveliest doll
you've ever seen?
-Take it, it's yours?
-I can't, I'm afraid of it.
And after I went to all
the trouble of making for you.
[scoffs]
-Toby, what have you become?
-What you see, Father.
I can do anything.
[electronic tinkling]
Hm?
Toby, stop it,
leave your father alone.
-I don't like this, my boy.
-From this moment on,
you will wear nothing but
the finest dresses, Mother.
[electronic zapping]
[loud gasp]
I don't want them, I don't
want them, leave me alone!
What are you trying
to do, Toby?
I can do anything.
Anything at all.
I have been given the power
to make you all happy
for the rest of your lives.
Father, that old pipe is your
prized possession, isn't it?
Well, I can turn
that pipe into gold.
Stop it!
These powers of yours, they're,
they're not right, Toby.
You can't find real happiness
by waving your hand,
and casting a magic spell.
[sighs] I should've know
you'd say something like that.
You haven't changed
a bit, Father.
Hm, oh.
Ah-ha! I knew it had to be you!
I knew it.
I knew it all the time.
Now I got you! [laughs]
Shh.
Hm?
[Toby blows]
[Karuku] Toby? Toby?
Mother, Father, Sherry!
You've got to hide.
Get out of here!
Ridiculous! This is our home,
what on earth should
we hide from?
-There's no time to explain--
-[Karuku] Toby?
-[gasping]
-Toby.
Toby, you're not being
lazy again, are you?
Toby! Toby!
My, my, Toby, imagine finding
you in a place like this?
Oh, those are people,
aren't they, Toby?
No, Lord Karuku,
these people are useless.
Oh Toby, you do
them a disservice,
I think they will make
delightful puppets.
[both groaning]
[thuds]
Now, are there any other
people in this house, Toby?
Er, none.
Well then, hurry up and do
to the rest of the village
what I just did
to this charming couple.
You won't keep me waiting,
will you, Toby?
[loud whizzing]
[high pitch zap]
[Sherry] Toby! Where are you?
Sherry, go and hide
yourself in the forest.
If you don't hide,
your brother-- [loud zap]
will have to turn you
into a living puppet.
[cries] Why are you doing to us?
Please, Toby, change Mother
and Father back again.
Change them back.
I'm sorry, Sherry, but I can't.
I don't know how.
Only Lord Kuruku
has the power
to change our mother
and father back.
I can only follow
my master's orders.
and so I must turn
all the villagers,
people of my own kind
into living puppets!
And in return
my master teaches me
another little
bit of his magic.
But some day Cheri,
when I'm the greatest
magician in the world
I will find the way
to repay you. I swear it!
[turbulent music]
[music ends]
[casual music]
[Cheri gasps and moans]
[gasps and moans]
Father! Mother!
They both going away somewhere.
They're all going away.
[music crescendo]
[Cheri panting]
I can't tell which is father
and mother anymore.
They're all going down
to the harbor.
I wonder why.
[Cheri] Let's follow them
and find out.
[Unico] All right.
[music continues]
[music ends]
Wait for me!
We've gotta get on that ship
with my parents.
[Unico] I wonder
where they taking everybody.
Nightmare Island.
[Yamaneko] Nightmare Island,
huh?
I heard bad things
about that place.
[Cheri gasps]
[Cheri and Unico moan]
[Cheri and Unico gasp]
Why is your boss wanna
carry all these things
to Nightmare Island for? Huh?
You'll find out
when we get there.
I wonder
where this ship is going.
I don't know but I hope
it gets there soon.
-[Unico] Whoa!
-[Cheri gasps]
Is Nightmare Island far?
No, not far at all.
You can see it already.
[lightning strikes]
[Yamaneko gasps]
[anticipatory music]
[music ends]
[casual music]
[Yamaneko sighs]
[Yamaneko sighs and laughs]
-Hurry Unico! Hurry!
-I'm coming!
Wow, I never seen anything
like this place.
[Yamaneko] Huh? What?
Well, I'll be a monkey's uncle.
We've got to try
and find Lord Kuruku.
Are you sure you know
what you're doing?
[Yamaneko]
Where they go?
Where? Ah,
there they are! [grunts]
[grunting]
[screams]
[music ends]
Excuse me!
Does anybody know where we can
find Lord Kuruku?
-[Unico and Cheri scream]
-[monster screams and grunts]
-[Cheri] Run!
-[Unico screams]
[monster grunts]
[tense music]
-[Cheri moaning]
-[monster grunting]
[monster screams]
Oh no! What is it?
I don't know
and I don't wanna find out!
-I think [indistinct] smell.
-[monster screams]
[monster grunts]
-[Cheri and Unico gasping]
-[monster screams]
-[Cheri gasps]
-[Unico moans]
[Cheri and Unico
panting and moaning]
[Cheri and Unico scream]
[music ends]
[monster screams]
[Cheri and Unico scream]
[Cheri screams]
[Cheri and Unico sigh]
[anticipation music]
Oh! I have house guests I see.
However did you
find your way in?
[Unico] Lord Kuruku!
Please, sir, I beg of you!
You beg of me?
Are you volunteering
to become living puppets?
That's very charitable of you.
Oh, you know
that's not what I mean.
Turning people
into puppets is a wicked thing!
You're a bad man!
[Kuruku laughing]
We'll aside from that,
am I the sort of person you
like to expend time with, huh?
Lord Kuruku you've got
to return my mother
and my father!
You're wasting your
time little girl
and what's worse
you're wasting mine.
Toby! Toby, come to me!
I'm here master.
I want you to deal
with these annoying pair
of little trespassers Toby.
- Huh? Cheri!
-Toby!
I beg a favor of you
Lord Kuruku.
My! This is a big day
for begging favors.
-What it is?
-They're only children master.
Please don't force me to turn
them into living puppets.
Well then,
what is that you propose?
As they're only children
let me turn them
into toys master.
Fine, fine, just get rid
of the little brats.
Thank you master.
[Cheri gasping and moaning]
[Cheri gasps]
Cheri, why didn't you listen
when I told you to hide
in the forest?
This is the weirdest
looking toy I ever saw.
[monster rattles]
Forgive me Cheri.
But you see,
I know the magic for toys.
Soon I'll change back
and carry you away
from this island.
[Yamaneko] Yeah, but doesn't
mean you have to do it
for this little run too.
[magic sound]
[both gasp]
[suspenseful music]
All right my little toys,
I'm in the mood to be amused.
[cheerful music]
[Kuruku screams] Oh!
[Kuruku screams]
[Kuruku grunting]
[Kuruku grunts]
[Kuruku gasps]
Stop, stop, get back everyone!
[music ends]
Toby, shouldn't you be at work?
-Yes master.
-You're not lying at me,
are you?
[casual music]
Huh? What? They're joints
made out of living puppets.
[screams] Hup-Hup!
[music continues]
I don't believe it!
The walls are getting
higher and higher. Wow!
[Kuruku laughing]
Better and better!
The greatest magic
castle in the world
and it's mine. [laughing]
Nothing can stop me.
Higher and higher
until its walls are made up
with every living creature
on the face of the earth.
[laughing]
[music ends]
[anticipation music]
[monster screams]
[music ends]
[melodic music]
[Cheri and Unico gasping]
-Toby!
-And now I have an appointment
to keep in the Valley
of the Demons.
The Valley of the Demons?
-What's that?
-I must go!
No Toby, stop! You have to save
our mother and father.
Come back here!
Toby!
What about our mother
and father?
[Unico] He's gone.
Where is
this Valley of the Demons?
Oh, no!
He's going there to turn
all them into living puppets.
-Come on, Unico.
-Where to?
We've got to go there too.
The Valley of the Demons?
We have to stop Toby.
We have to warn the demons
before they're all turned
into living puppets.
[Unico grunting and moaning]
Do we have to? [moans]
[chaotic music]
[music ends]
[silence]
[tense music]
[music ends]
[Cheri panting]
-Hello! Is anybody home?
-Hello!
It's so quiet.
[sighs] Hello?
[Cheri and Unico screaming]
[Unico] Oh!
Who turned out the light?
[Cheri] Unico, where are you?
[Unico grunting]
-[Unico grunts]
-What's wrong, Unico?
[Unico grunts] Be
quiet for a minute,
I'm trying to light up.
[Cheri gasps]
I can't believe it!
-[Unico struggling grunts]
-[Cheri gasps]
That's wonderful, Unico!
I had no idea you could do
anything like that.
[struggling grunts] I have
to work at it or it goes out.
[Cheri] Is anybody here?
It looks like they've all gone.
Toby must've turned
them into puppets
and taken them away.
[crying in the distance]
Listen!
-What? What is it?
-[Unico hushes]
-I hear something.
-[crying in the distance]
It's over there!
What do you think it could be?
[Unico] It sounds like crying.
But who could be crying.
[crying in the distance]
[Cheri] Hello! Who's there?
[Unico] Oh! Here they are.
[Cheri] Those are baby demons.
So he wasn't able
to find you, huh?
What happen to your parents?
[all crying and moaning]
He took all the mothers
and fathers away.
We all hid down
here in this hole
and now we are alone.
[all moaning]
It was my brother
who did this to you.
Oh, forgive me! [crying]
[all sobbing and screaming]
Stop it everyone!
Oh! When you cry
like that it makes me--
[moaning and sobbing]
[Unico] Oh!
[yawns]
Oh, please stop it!
Stop crying, oh!
I'm so sorry!
I promise I'll bring
your parents back to you.
Wherever they are,
I'll bring them back.
I promise.
How are you going to do that?
We have no idea
how to fight Kuruku’s magic.
There must be someone,
somewhere who would know.
The Sphinx who knows everything
would probably know that too.
The what that knows everything?
Of course she'd know!
Hey listen,
if anybody know how to fight
his magic the Sphinx would.
Well then,
where's exactly is the Sphinx
who knows everything?
-[demon 1 grunts]
-[Unico] Hey!
Stop it! Let me go.
[demon 1 grunts]
-This is serious business you--
-[demon 1 grunts]
Oh! Cut it up!
What's wrong with you?
Cheri, we've got
to find this Sphinx,
she's the only chance
that we've got.
She's over there.
You don't have far to go!
We'll go and see the Sphinx
and I promise we'll bring
your parents back to you.
Don't worry!
[Unico] We'll be back soon.
So be brave!
And don't cry!
Mama! Mama!
Mama! Mama! Mama!
[all crying] Mama! Mama!
[wind blowing]
Unico, forgive me.
I know I should never have
to drag you into all this.
[sighs] Where do you think
the Sphinx could be?
[Cheri] How could anyone
live in a place like this?
[Unico grunts]
Come on, Cheri.
You're right,
we have to find her.
For my mother and father sake.
But I'm so tired.
So tired.
[Cheri moans]
[Unico moaning]
I can't go...
-...much further.
-Who goes there?
Who dares trespass on my desert?
Go away!
Hey, answer me!
Are you two all right?
[Mars worries]
[emotional music]
I've never seen anything
like you.
What are you?
[Mars grunts]
[grunts] Huh!
I'm not so sure
you're even worth to saving.
[Mars sighs]
[grunting] This one
is more like it!
I'll be more than happy
to save your life. [laughing]
Hmm, so you came all this way
into the desert just
to see the Sphinx, huh?
Yes, we got to see her.
But she could be anywhere.
Can you help us?
You see,
the Sphinx is my mother.
But she's out visiting friends,
so I'm in charge.
Oh, so you mean
the Sphinx isn't even here?
And after we've come
all this way.
Don't look so depressed,
anything you wanna know
just ask me, I know everything!
Do you know how to fight
Kuruku's magic powers?
Kuruku? What's that?
Anyway I'm not expected
to know about magic yet.
Ask me something simpler.
We’re in trouble Cheri.
[Cheri moans]
Oh, wait a minute!
I bet the great Trojan Horse
will be able to help
you fight this guy magic powers.
My mother said that he knows
almost as much she does.
The Trojan Horse?
You got it! The Trojan Horse
at the End of the Earth!
[blowing wind]
But listen, the End of the Earth
is a long, long,
long way from here.
But that's where you find him.
[Cheri] Could he really be
the one to tell me
how to get my mother
and father back?
But nobody is ever been able
to make it
to the End of the Earth.
Hey! Where do you think
you're going?
[grunts] I tell you,
you're crazy!
Hey, do you think you can just
walk to the End of the Earth?
They're nuts. Hey, stop!
[Mars sighs] Hey!
Come back! You'll never make it!
You can walk for years,
and years,
and years and still not
even get close to it.
[Cheri] That may be,
but I have to try.
-Unico!
-Yes, Cheri?
This is where we go
our separate ways.
[laughs] Our separate ways?
What do you mean?
Just what she said bone head.
Can't you see that the lady
is trying to tell you goodbye?
Goodbye? But is that mean
that she's leaving me here?
No! I won't stay here!
I'm coming with you
to the End of the Earth!
-Unico?
-[Unico] Hmm?
Thank you for coming
along with me this far
but now I'll have
to go all alone.
-I can't take you with me.
-Why not?
-[Cheri] Just because.
-[Unico] Because why?
Unico...
-Goodbye!
-Cheri!
-Stop following me,
-Cheri, what's wrong with you?
What's wrong?
She doesn't like me anymore.
-Oh yeah?
-That's right!
She's living me behind,
isn't she?
[Mars] Bone head, she not only
likes ya, she loves ya.
No she doesn't.
If she did,
she wouldn't go away and...
leave me here. She wouldn't.
Is because she loves you
that she's making you stay here.
She doesn't want you
to have to suffer too.
She's gonna find the End
of the World all by herself.
-She's really something else.
-[sighs] You're right!
Cheri!
Wait Cheri!
You do love me! You do!
And I love you!
I can help you Cheri!
I can!
[confidant music]
What? What's happen
to the little guy?
Hey slow down!
Is that or you'll fly right
right of the End of the Earth!
[Cheri stammers] I'm sorry,
I couldn't take
you with me Unico.
I'll miss you already.
Oh Unico, goodbye.
[Cheri gasps]
Who are you? Are you taking
me to the End of the Earth?
Hey wait a minute! Wait for me!
As long as you're going that way
take me with you!
[Mars screams]
At this rate
we'll be there in no time.
Oh no! If you here
that means you let Unico
back there all alone.
Unico? Oh I think
he's all right-whoa!
Oh, what could've
happen to Unico?
[music continues]
Do we still have
a long way to go?
A long, long way.
And I'm getting hungry.
Unico and Toby,
mother and father,
I wonder what's happen to them.
I'm so alone.
[screams]
We're almost there!
[music ends]
Is this the End of the Earth?
You've got it!
And I know just where to look
for the Trojan Horse,
my mother told me once. Come on!
Hurry up!
Thank you!
[Cheri and Mars gasp]
[Cheri gasps] Unico it's you!
I should've know that we never
could've been separated.
-Thank you.
-I can't believe it.
Okay, okay, let's go!
Are you gonna stand there
all day holding him like that?
Come on!
Why is there is so much
old junk here?
[Mars] Because it's
the End of the Earth.
All the things that nobody wants
get washed up here.
[Mars screams]
Oh, look! Here comes
some more junk now, huh?
[sighs] No wonder somebody
threw this away. [screams]
-[Mars screams]
-How sad.
This junk could've been fix up
almost good as new.
So this is what happens
to all the things nobody wants.
-But where is the Trojan Horse?
-I know!
Hey, Trojan Horse!
Where are you?
This certainly
isn't the Trojan Horse.
-[object 1] You're a human!
-[Cheri gasps]
Who said that?
-[lantern] A human!
-[vase] Yes a human!
-[carriage] A human?
-[object 2] A human!
[drum] A human!
Just like the ones
that threw us away!
[all objects] It's a human!
A human! A human!
All quit your bellyaching!
All of you shut up!
[Mars grunts]
Oh, where could
the Trojan Horse be?
- Was someone looking for me?
-[Cheri gasps]
-Where are you?
-[Trojan Horse] Well, I...
I'm right under you, young lady.
[gasps] Pardon me!
[grunts] Is that you?
I'm the Trojan Horse.
Wow! What a mess of a horse!
[Trojan Horse] Am I really
that filthy?
You bet you are.
You're disgusting.
-Isn't it?
-Yep.
[Trojan Horse] Well,
I'm not surprised,
it's been over a thousand years
since anyone bother
to give me a good cleaning.
Oh, that's all right! If we
just dusty you off...[coughs]
You'll be as good as new. See?
[Trojan Horse] I thank
you, young lady.
[sighs] I feel better already!
I'd almost forgotten
what it was like to have
someone take care of me.
[Cheri] There you go.
[coughing]
Would you might terribly if we
asked you a question Mr. Horse?
[Trojan Horse] It's about
Lord Kuruku, isn't it?
Why don't you take a pick
in my eye young lady?
In your eye?
[casual music]
Then you already know
about Kuruku?
[Trojan Horse laughs] You'd be
surprise that what I know
and what I can reveal to you
when you look in my eye.
-[all sigh]
-[Trojan Horse] Very well...
I'll tell you
the story of Kuruku.
Long, long ago
Kuruku washed up here
just like all the others things
you see about you.
[Mars] Look! It's a puppet.
[Trojan Horse] Yes,
once upon a time
Kuruku was a marionette
but unhappily he fell
into the hands
of some very bad people.
[Unico] Bad people?
[Trojan Horse] Yes.
A mean tempered old woman
and a wicked magician.
They mistreated Kuruku terribly,
they pulled
and yank at his strings.
And when they finally
became a tangled mess
they simply threw him away.
[Cheri] They throw him away?
[Trojan Horse] As if he was
so much garbage.
And after countless years
floating in the sea
he washed up here
at the End of the Earth.
-[Unico] Look a beam of light!
-[Cheri] What is it?
[Trojan Horse] There's only
one spot in the land
at the end of the Earth
where the sun shines.
And then for only
a few moments every day.
That is the spot
where Kuruku ended up.
And after 200 or 300 years
of this a strange thing happen.
[Cheri] He's beginning to move!
[Trojan Horse] Just so.
The light of the sun is full
of mysterious powers.
But at the same time,
it woke him for his long sleep
it candled in him a burning
hatred of humanity.
For it was humanity
that it throw him away.
And so one day,
he left the land of the End of
the Earth in search for revenge.
So how can we fight
Kuruku's magic?
-[Trojan Horse] I don't know.
-[all] What?
[Trojan Horse] I only know
that your courage
and love are the best
weapons against him.
[both] Huh?
Is that all you can say?
That is all I can say.
You must fight his evil
with your goodness.
And you won't know
which is the stronger
until the battle is over.
Right, let's go find out!
[Cheri] Thank you Mr. Horse!
[Trojan Horse] Goodbye
my children.
[confidant music]
What's sort of a place
are we going to?
It's called Nightmare Island.
[cheers] That sounds
like my kind of a place.
[Cheri] There it is!
[Mars] Yeah? It doesn't look
all that scary. [moans]
[music ends]
Okay, so where's
this Kuruku fella?
Come on, let me at him.
Just let me at him, huh!
Huh? Hey, I don't know
but I think
maybe I've found him.
[gasps] Is he already?
-[monster grunts]
-Hey you big jerk,
what a fat lip.
[monster and Mars scream]
[moans] Wait a minute!
[Mars and Cheri scream]
[anticipatory music]
-[monster screams]
-[Cheri and Mars screaming]
[Mars panting]
Hey I think we lost him.
So hey, was that Kuruku guy?
No, it wasn't.
-[monster screaming]
-[Unico, Mars and Cheri scream]
[monster grunts]
-Quick, this way.
-Come on!
-[Cheri panting]
-[Mars screaming]
-[Mars] Hey!
-[Cheri gasps]
[all screaming]
[all panting]
This ain’t my idea
of a good time.
[Kuruku] Is never a moments rest
around here recently.
Who is it this time?
Why it feels two insufferable
brats I met not long ago?
Why on earth they run
around you supposed.
-[Cheri gasps]
-[Mars] Let's get out of here!
-But where do we go?
-We stay here!
Run for your lives!
No, we got to stick together.
I may be mistaken,
but didn't I have you both...
-turned into toys?
-Yes.
I even danced for you.
-[Cheri gasps]
-[Kuruku laughing]
I think perhaps Toby is playing
a trick on me, hmm?
Please Kuruku, you can't keep
everyone as your puppet forever.
That's right,
you've got to turn them back.
-[Kuruku grunting]
-[Unico screams]
Why should I, little one?
Why you're try to frighten me?
Toby, I like a word with you!
Toby!
-Yes, sir.
-[Kuruku] Not you idiot.
Yes, Lord Kuruku,
you have need of me?
Explain yourself!
Cheri!
What she's doing here?
I've had enough!
How do I get out of here?
[Yamaneko and Mars grunting]
-[Mars screams]
-[Yamaneko grunts]
Who was that?
Let me out! Let me out of here!
[Kuruku] Well, Toby to bring
this game to an end
I suppose you should have to
turn them into living puppets.
Toby?
Did you hear what I said?
There's really no other option
open to us now, is there?
Toby!
I ordered you to turn them
into living puppets, now!
You forget that I am human too,
Lord Kuruku.
Yes, so you are!
[tense music]
And it's amazing to me
that I've never held
that against you.
I've been waiting for the day
when you turn me
into a puppet as well.
I think that day has come,
after all you're no
longer of any use to me
if you won't obey orders, Toby.
You leave me no choice.
-Run Cheri, run fast as you can!
-I won't!
Do you really think
you're match for me?
-How interesting!
-Run Cheri. [grunts]
I won't run!
No matter what you say,
I won't leave you, I won't!
You little fool.
This is no place for you.
[Toby grunting and groaning]
Very well master.
See how you like this!
[laughing] Somehow I believe
you have to do a lot better
than that. [laughing]
There's more
where that came from.
What? [grunting]
[Kuruku screams]
[tense music continues]
[Toby moans]
[Toby groaning and grunting]
[Toby sighs]
Toby! [gasps]
Toby!
[crying and moaning]
[gasps]
I don't want you to think
that I've forgotten you,
little girl.
I won't run away Kuruku.
But I want to know,
why do you have
to do such bad things?
Because that the only things
he can do.
He's never done
a good thing in his life.
Please Kuruku,
won't you turn everyone back?
Yeah, turn them back.
My, what a couple of courageous
little creatures you are.
Aren't you a least
frightened of me?
-Actually, I'm terrified of you.
-And so am I.
Marvelous,
that's the nicest thing
-anyone have said to me all day.
-And...
-there's something else.
-[Kuruku] Go ahead.
This is a terrible
life you're living
when frightening
people makes you happy.
I'm living a terrible life,
am I? [laughing]
You don't know how happy
you're making me.
Please don't stop now.
-It feels wonderful!
-Stop it please,
-you shouldn't frighten people.
-Leave her alone!
[Kuruku laughing]
How delightful!
And to think once upon a time
I had to hide
my hatred of humans.
I had to dance when they wanted
to me to dance.
And smile when they wanted
to me to smile.
But no longer,
times have changed and the shoe
is on the other foot.
Isn't now, hmm?
-Kuruku listen--
-[screams] Shut up!
No longer do I take orders
from humans.
Your time has come.
-Stop!
-No Unico!
Unico run!
Now I just have a little
cleaning up to do outside,
my day will be complete.
[silence]
[Unico grunting]
[struggling grunts]
Cheri! Cheri! [crying]
[Cheri laughs] Unico!
Is that you, Unico?
-[Unico cries]
- Unico !
[Unico crying]
Cheri.
[Cheri] Unico,
please forgive me.
I should never have brought you
to such an evil place.
Unico run!
[Kuruku laughing]
Huh? Kuruku!
[anticipatory music]
[Yamaneko screams]
-Kuruku!
-Stop it! [grunts]
Stay away from me,
I had about enough of this.
Huh? [screams]
What's the big idea?
Look what you've
done to my tail.
[screams]
[grunts]
[Kuruku laughing]
There, I think that takes care
of all the little
annoyances for today.
[Unico] Not quite Kuruku.
Who's that?
What a resilient little fellow.
You're not finished
until you taken care of me.
[tense music continues]
[monster screaming]
Kuruku is time
you let your puppets go.
You intolerable little
rotten muffin, how dare you?
[Unico screams]
[laughs] He's fast,
I haven't had this
much fun in years.
[moans] I don't what I can do.
Maybe if I just keep on running
I can tire him out.
No matter where you are
you cannot escape.
[Kuruku laughing]
[screams]
[Unico sighing]
-[Unico screaming]
-[Kuruku laughing and screaming]
-I've got you now! [laughing]
-[Unico screams]
[Unico moaning]
[Unico screams]
[grunts and moans]
There is nowhere left to go.
I let everybody down.
And so the curtain falls
you little pain in the neck.
[Unico screams]
[moans and screams]
[Kuruku sighs]
[Kuruku sighing]
[Kuruku grunts]
-[Unico sighs]
-[Kuruku] I'll kill you!
[silence]
[Kuruku laughing]
Well, that was certainly
very exciting. [laughing]
[Unico] Kuruku!
-[Kuruku sighs]
-Please Kuruku,
break the spell
and release all your puppets.
If you don't,
I'll be force to fight you
and I might have to...
destroy you
and I rather not do that.
Why you insignificant
little brat--
I am through playing
games with you!
[Unico grunts]
[anticipatory music]
How do you like that?
Now you have no place to run,
you've fallen in glue pot.
I don't plan on running anymore.
You leave me no choice
but to fight you Kuruku.
I'll struggle to hide my terror.
Prepare to die!
[Unico screams] Ya!
[tragic music]
[Kuruku screams]
-[Kuruku screams]
-[Unico moaning]
[Unico moaning and grunting]
I should've known I never
stand a chance against him.
[Kuruku screams and grunts]
What are you talking about?
This is more than a scratch.
But I had no idea
I hardly touched you.
I'm sorry.
[sighs] Why are you saying
that your sorry?
Why?
-Because I feel sorry for you.
-You feel?
What do you mean
you feel sorry for me?
I'm sorry
that you're full of... [grunts]
so much hate.
You think that all people
are your enemies
but that's only because
you've never had a friend.
Did you say 'a friend'?
I know how important
friends are.
-That's why I understand you.
-[Kuruku gasps]
Please, stop it.
The idea of me
being someone's friend...
it's making me feel
quite ill. [screams]
I know what happen
to you long ago.
I know that some people
treated you badly.
If you had a friend you'd know
that not everyone is like that.
You must be very lonely.
Lonely!
He says that I'm lonely!
But don't you understand?
I hate people!
I do! [grunts and cries]
[Unico grunts]
What's wrong Kuruku?
How can you be so cruel?
All this talk of friendship
and understand
is making me feel
all soft and gooey.
[screams]
I live only to hate humanity
and now you tell me
that I'm lonely,
that people are good.
Like a I need a friend.
Your words are melting my heart.
[Kuruku screams]
Kuruku don't worry
I'll be your friend, okay?
[Kuruku screams]
If you free all the puppets
from your magic spell
-I'll be your friend forever.
-[Kuruku screams]
That word again.
Who would ever want
to be a friend of mine?
Who?
[sad music continues]
Oh, wait Kuruku
don't be frighten.
Anyone can have a friend,
really.
It's too late for me I'm afraid.
-[Kuruku grunts and moans]
-Kuruku!
[Kuruku grunts and moans]
[Unico] What's happening?
[Kuruku] My hatred was
the only thing
that kept me alive.
You've taken it from me,
I have nothing left.
But for the first time
in my life
I can hardly say it...
I feel good!
[emotive music]
-[woman] Unico!
-What?
Did someone called me? [moans]
Unico my child it's time
to you to leave this place.
-Leave?
-Yes.
The gods will soon discover
what you've done here.
I must take you
some place far away
where they cannot find you.
But why?
Because that is your faith,
Unico.
Come.
[calm music]
May I at least
to say goodbye to Cheri?
She will never forget you.
Cheri, goodbye.
[emotional music]
-[Cheri] Mother!
-Cheri.
-Father...
-Toby.
Unico?
Unico!
[sighs]
Hmm good as new. Huh?
[Yamaneko] You get back here!
Wofa! Twida!
Wait up!
[Cheri panting]
Unico?
[sighs]
Unico...
[emotional music]