[LITTENHEIM] The golden haired
brat has led his fleet
out of the Imperial capital.
Additionally, he had the nerve
to refer to us all
as "traitors."
A title that blatantly
calls for our subjugation!
[NOBLES murmuring]
I hear you, men.
Fret not.
We are the Lippstadt
Nobles Coalition.
And we shall use this
opportunity to finally
put that upstart in his place.
We will dispatch forces
in multiple positions
along the corridor to Geiersburg
Fortress and chip away
at his numbers piece by piece.
Once he is weakened,
we will strike his few
remaining forces all at once
and completely annihilate
every last one of them.
To the great god Odin,
we ask that you
grant us your protection!
[NOBLES]
For Victory will be ours!
[cheering, laughter]
[MERKATZ]
Wait a moment.
Dividing our forces would not
be in our best interests.
[BRAUNSCHWEIG] Hmm...
Then what do you suggest we do?
Concentrate our forces
here at Geiersburg
to intercept the enemy
and overwhelm them.
Bah! Drag the brat
out to our fortress?
Well, it's true we would have
the positional advantage.
Indeed, sir.
[STADEN] No. There exists
an even better way.
[STADEN] We would still
want to draw the enemy
to Geiersburg, but while their
men are here, we send a second,
detached force to capture
the Imperial capital of Odin.
And once we have
taken the capital,
the emperor will be in
our possession as well.
--[NOBLES gasping]
--That could work. Allow me.
Let the man finish.
[STADEN] Finally, we'll have the
young emperor declare
that Marquis Reinhard von
Lohengramm is the traitor.
And with an endorsement
from royalty,
our position will effectively
reverse with our enemy's.
With nowhere left to go,
the golden haired parvenu
will become an orphan in space.
[NOBLES laughing]
[STADEN]
Hmph.
Simply fantastic!
A strategy befitting the true
heirs to the Goldenbaum Dynasty!
I would be honored
if you would permit me
to lead the second,
detached force!
[NOBLE 18E]
No, let me!
[NOBLE 18F]
Please sir, allow me to do it!
[NOBLE 18G]
Let me carry out the plan!
[HILDESHEIM]
Admiral Staden.
I would like a word with you.
[MERKATZ]
That plan is foolish.
[SCHNEIDER]
What do you mean?
From a purely
militaristic perspective,
it seems viable to me.
And it may be viable,
but not for this coalition.
They're thinking only
of the power they'd gain
if they were to succeed.
And they're desperate
to outdo each other.
Without unwavering trust between
the primary forces
and the detached force,
that strategy is
destined for failure.
Is that why Marquis
Lohengramm left Odin empty?
Either way, Admiral.
There are some among
the nobles who are already
preparing for battle.
They're hoping to get ahead
of the others and increase
their own chances of
leading the detached force.
Aren't you going
to try to stop them?
It's impossible to restrain
the egos of noblemen.
It's pointless.
They wouldn't listen.
No matter how I warn them.
So you're saying they
need to be defeated,
and only then will they
truly learn their lesson?
The traitors are finally
making their move.
Oh? So it's started at last.
[REINHARD]
My spy has informed me that
their vanguard
commander is Staden.
Familiar? He should be.
I believe he taught you
tactical theory in school.
Tell me. Will we win?
Staden is a smart man
with abundant knowledge.
However, he tends to lean
too heavily on theory.
Back when I was a cadet,
we'd frequently
ridicule him when that
proved to be his undoing.
[REINHARD]
Hmph. Very well, Mittermeyer.
Deploy to the Altena Starzone
as our advance guard,
and have a reunion
with your teacher.
Sir!
[NARRATOR]
In the year UC 797,
or the 488th year of
the Imperial Calendar,
on April 19, a conflict
that would later be called
the Lippstadt War began.
[NARRATOR] In hopes of earning
the right of leadership
in the operation to
capture the emperor,
two deployed before
the other nobles.
Hildesheim and Staden.
[NARRATOR] But a minefield,
laid by the Mittermeyer Fleet
beforehand
impeded their course.
[TACTICAL OFFICER 18A]
Compressed data received
from patrol craft T07.
Movement of the
Hildesheim Fleet confirmed
on the enemy's left flank.
The Staden Fleet has also begun
to move on the right flank.
[NARRATOR] In order to break
through the Alliance Navy's
minefield during
the Battle of Amritsar,
Reinhard's forces had deployed
directional Seffle particles.
However, the Hildesheim
and Staden fleets
did not have access
to this technology.
With nowhere else to go, both
fleets were forced to detour
around the minefield
to its left and right.
[ARMSDORF]
They're on the move.
I've been waiting for this.
They must know we're not going
to sit in one place forever.
All right, our fleet will also
begin its advance!
We are now
entering the minefield!
This way seems clear,
but those are live mines.
If we slip off course
even the slightest bit.
[NAVI. OFFICER 18B]
Admiral Mittermeyer has trained
this fleet himself--
have some faith.
[NARRATOR] The Mittermeyer Fleet
passed through a cleared route
so narrow that Staden's Fleet
didn't even see it,
and succeeded in striking the
Hildesheim Fleet from behind.
Impossible!
The minefield was
active, we checked!
So how did they get through?
[MITTERMEYER]
Swift movement is our specialty.
They should've known as much.
Fire away!
[HILDESHEIM screams]
[TACTICAL OFFICER 18B] The
propulsion engine's been hit!
We're losing control!
[TACTICAL OFFICER 18C]
We've lost contact with
the Hildesheim Fleet!
How could this be happening?
Given our numbers, we have no
real chance of winning now.
We'll retreat. Head to
Rentenberg and request aid.
[ARMSDORF]
The Staden Fleet seems to be
leaving the starzone.
He got away, huh? Impressive.
At least my former teacher
knows when he's been beaten.
[NARRATOR]
With Staden's retreat
and Hildesheim's
forces defeated,
the first clash of the Lippstadt
War, the Battle of Altena,
ended in victory
for Mittermeyer.
He what?
Not only did he lose, but he
fled to Rentenberg, as well?
That fortress is
a vital logistics center.
We must avoid losing control
of it by any means necessary!
[BRAUNSCHWEIG growls]
[OVLESSER]
Hmm.
[SCHNEIDER] It ended just
the way you said it would.
Do we have any real hope of
defeating Marquis Lohengramm?
[SCHNEIDER]
Admiral, what are fighting for?
Tell me, for who's sake
are we fighting them?
[MERKATZ]
Stop it.
[grunts]
All you or I can do
at this point is defend
our honor as soldiers.
Nothing more.
[SCHNEIDER sighs]
[MITTERMEYER]
I apologize, sir.
Staden was able to escape me.
[REINHARD] No matter. Our
goal was to put a damper
on their spirits,
and we achieved that.
We know where
they fled when they left
the Altena Starzone.
Staden lead his fleet to
the Rentenberg Fortress,
which is a key location
on the front lines.
The strength of
its garrison force
should not be ignored.
[REINHARD]
Hmm. Then here's the plan.
We'll take Rentenberg Fortress
and make it our bridgehead for
taking down Geiersburg.
Reuenthal. Mittermeyer.
Occupy Rentenberg
and take control
without doing any damage.
[BOTH]
Sir!
[OBERSTEIN] Rentenberg Fortress
gets all of its energy
from a power reactor
located in its center.
The only way to get there is
via the number six passage.
Once this reactor
is under our control,
we will we be able to take over
all functions of the fortress.
Looks like we'll have to
use hand-to-hand combat.
It's not as simple
as they think.
You can say that again.
I can't say I'm surprised.
They filled it with
Seffle particles.
He's a barbarian.
And he wants a primitive
fight to the death.
Of course, he's Rentenberg's
defense commander.
If it was anyone else,
it'd be easy.
[yells]
[gasps]
[groans]
That man might as well
have been brought into
this world to beat
people to death.
[SOLDIER 18B yells]
[OVLESSER growls]
[SOLDIER 18C screams]
[SOLDIER 18D groans]
[SOLDIER 18E grunts]
[MITTERMEYER] "The Armored
Grenadier Commander."
High Admiral Ovlesser.
[SOLDIER 18F groans]
[SOLDIER 18G grunts]
[MITTERMEYER] They have
been fighting in full armor
for upwards of eight hours, now.
[REUENTHAL] It appears they're
using some kind of drug.
I understand the situation.
Ovlesser may be courageous,
but he is also a Neanderthal.
If we let him live,
he'll be of no use,
and I'm absolutely certain
he wouldn't want to be
kept alive at our mercy.
Give him a glorious death.
[BOTH]
Sir.
--[ARMSDORF] Your Excellency.
--[REUENTHAL grunts]
[ARMSDORF] Transmission
from the enemy commander.
Transmission?
Connect him to me.
[ARMSDORF]
Yes, sir. But, well...
It's fine.
Hello, golden-haired brat!
Do you have the guts
to look me in the eye,
even through a screen?
You may have been
born into good fortune,
but you've achieved nothing.
Now you want the Imperial Navy?
I will never allow a child such
as yourself to control that!
And the idea that
you'd take advantage
of the emperor's
favor to monopolize
the Imperial government
is outrageous!
Despite your lowly birth,
both you and your sister
deceived the previous emperor
with sex, and your good looks!
That kind of insolence
is worthy of death!
Cut the transmission!
[COMMS. OFFICER 13A]
Right!
Reuenthal! Mittermeyer!
[BOTH]
Sir!
[REINHARD] Drag that foolish,
obscene oaf before me!
Tch! Yes. Don't
you dare kill him.
Bring him alive, if you
have to rip off his limbs!
I'm going to tear that
bastard's filthy mouth
to shreds with my own two hands!
[BOTH]
Sir!
This can't be good.
Indeed.
It seems as though
His Excellency
is a creature of
emotion as well.
Armsdorf, bring the commander
of the engineering corps here.
Also. I have one more request.
[gasps]
[SOLDIER 18I groans]
[OVLESSER] Come at me if
you dare, you cowardly rats!
I'll throw all your corpses in a
pot and make you into fricassee!
Though I imagine
you'd taste rather foul,
being the lowly
peasants that you are!
[OVLESSER growls]
[REUENTHAL]
I guess barbarians don't know
the meaning of moderation.
[OVLESSER]
"Bewitching Eyes" Reuenthal
and the Gale Wolf
show themselves.
Grown impatient with the
incompetence of your men?
You truly think the two of
you alone can defeat me?
Well, we won't
know until we try.
We're both admirals
and you're a high admiral.
I'd say we're a good matchup.
[OVLESSER]
So you do know your place!
Out of respect
for your courtesy,
I'll pass the fleet
admiral's baton to you.
You can collect it in Valhalla!
[OVLESSER yells]
[growls]
[yells]
Is that all you've got?!
Why run?
Do it, now!
[OVLESSER grunts]
[screams]
[OVLESSER groaning]
[growls]
You damn cowards!
[REUENTHAL]
We'll take that as a compliment.
Ovlesser's been taken down,
we have no use for
the rest of them.
Proceed to take the area!
[ARMSDORF]
Sir!
[NARRATOR] Thus, control of the
number six passage was seized
while it was still bathed in
the blood of their comrades.
[OVLESSER]
Hmm...
What are you doing here?
Oberstein?
I've come to set
High Admiral Ovlesser free.
[BOTH gasp]
[MITTERMEYER]
What? That's ridiculous.
Do you know how many
of our men died
trying to capture that beast?
[OBERSTEIN]
Know that I am acting
with Marquis
Lohengramm's approval.
Speaking of...
His Excellency has deeply
acknowledged your efforts.
Is that not sufficient for you?
[MITTERMEYER grunts]
[OBERSTEIN] For the time being,
I would like you all to leave me
alone with our captive.
[OBERSTEIN]
Now. High Admiral Ovlesser.
We would like you to return to
the Lippstadt Nobles Coalition
and act as our
messenger of sorts.
You're serious?
That I am.
No matter which
side wins this civil war,
it will inevitably cause
the Empire great harm.
And Marquis Lohengramm
does not wish to see
the Empire as a whole
grow fragile and weak.
We'd like for you to give us
a third option in resolving
this conflict, to help
us end it quickly.
Feh! Do you really think
there's a chance our leader
will agree to make peace now?
If it comes from such
a distinguished warrior
as yourself, perhaps
even they will consider it.
I understand what you're saying.
But... If I do return
to Geiersburg,
you realize you
have no guarantee
that I'll do what
the brat wants.
[OVLESSER sighs]
You must be High Admiral
Ovlesser, am I correct?
You can't tell just
by looking at me?
Right this way.
Our leader awaits you.
High Admiral Ovlesser.
You made it back in one piece.
Sir!
Do you know what happened
to the rest of your men?
Because interestingly enough,
they were all captured
and publicly put to death.
Wait, they were executed?
[BRAUNSCHWEIG] Why then, I
wonder, were you the only one
who was set free and
allowed to return here?
--[guns cocking]
--[gasps]
[OVLESSER growls]
Hold on.
This must be a trap--the
golden-haired brat set this up
to trick every one of us!
Silence, you traitor!
[OVLESSER gasps]
You were the only one
to return alive because
you obviously sold
yourself out to the enemy!
Tell me, what did
you promise him?!
That you would bring him my
severed head on a stake?!
That's not true!
I have done nothing
to betray you!
This is simply a trap!
As I said, the brat must have
set this up to trick us all!
Shoot! Shoot at him, you idiots!
--[gunshots]
--[OVLESSER grunts, groans]
You fools. This is
what he wants to happen!
[GUARDS groaning]
[OVLESSER]
Why don't you get it?!
--It's a trap!
--[grunting]
[groans]
--[GUARD 18C gasps]
--[OVLESSER] A ruse!
[gasping]
I swear, I did not betray you!
Kill him! Kill him at once!
I did not betray--
[gasps]
That boy intends to defeat
anyone who doubts him.
He will eradicate all who
are stuck in the past.
[gunshot]
[OVLESSER]
He will... eradicate all.
[BRAUNSCHWEIG]
The damned fool...
What shall we say was
the cause of his demise?
We need an
official statement.
We'll call it what
it was, an execution.
He betrayed his comrades
and was punished.
Make sure the
whole Empire knows!
[ANSBACH] Don't make
such a resentful face.
You're not the only one
who doesn't know
what tomorrow will bring.
Perhaps you'll be
grateful that you died
before this day came to an end.
[OBERSTEIN] The man believed
to despise us the most
has now been
executed as a traitor.
This will foster agitation and
mistrust amongst the nobles.
From their perspective,
anyone could betray them.
[NARRATOR]
In the year UC 797,
or the 488th year of the
Imperial Calendar, in May,
Reinhard took control
of Rentenberg Fortress
and subsequently advanced the
war against the coalition
of nobles even further.
[TACTICAL OFFICER 13C]
Ship spotted ahead.
ID code known.
It's the Fezzan
merchant ship Berezka.
It's possible it's
carrying the nobles
who have escaped.
Let's inspect it, then.
Tell them to stop.
[TACTICAL OFFICER 13C]
It's just migrant farmers
and their families.
We don't see anybody
who looks suspicious here.
Money is tight for all of us,
so he's transporting
us as cargo.
As cargo? All of you?
You have several
women and children.
Is there anything that you need?
[KONEV gasps]
We're low on medicine,
as well as milk for
the babies on board.
I understand.
I'll have some delivered.
And please,
do take care of yourselves.
[KONEV]
Thank you so much for your help.
[sighing]
We managed to get
through that in one piece.
Well, we couldn't
outright tell them
that we're carrying Terra's
faithful on a pilgrimage.
That Kircheis.
I could tell he's a good man.
[KONEV]
Honestly, I pity him.
Good men such
as him never live long.
Especially not
in times like these.
[NARRATOR] Next time on
Legend of the Galactic Heroes:
Die Neue These: Episode 19,
"The Battle of
the Doria Starzone."