[YANG]
From this point forward,
our fleet will head
for Shampool.
While they may be traitors,
before we engage in combat
with fellow Alliancemen, there's
something I'd like to say.
[YANG]
Not long ago when visiting
the capital planet Heinessen,
I made a request
of Space Fleet
Commander-in-Chief Bewcock.
He then granted me a decree.
It states that in the event of
a coup d'état such as this,
our fleet would strike it down
and restore law and order.
[JULIAN gasps]
[JULIAN] I don't quite
understand why we're going
to Shampool
instead of Heinessen.
It's simple.
They could disrupt both our
communications and supply lines.
To prevent that, we need to
establish new supply bases
while we still can.
I see. But no
matter what they do,
their commander
isn't Yang Wen-li.
That's true, but there
may be a future Yang Wen-li.
I mean, who even knew
the name before the battle
of El Facil, right?
If we weren't at war,
no one would know who I am.
I'd still just be an aspiring
historian in some library.
Yes, but instead,
you've become one
of the subjects for
historians to study.
You know,
I've heard that Yang Wen-li
is apparently a pretty big deal.
Funny that we both
share the same name
when we're nothing alike.
[JULIAN chuckles]
That humility is exactly what
makes you so respectable.
Most people'd be lost in
their own self-importance
if they were in your position.
Julian, you shouldn't flatter
your superiors so much.
The weak-willed will
start to believe you
and they'll ruin
themselves in the process.
[JULIAN laughs]
Yes. Understood, sir.
Well, as long as we're clear.
[NARRATOR] On April 26th
of the year UC 797,
the Yang Fleet began its assault
on the planet Shampool.
As the traitors on Shampool
had no garrison fleet,
the battle was fought
primarily on the ground.
With the Rosen
Ritter at the helm,
Yang's ground forces
subjugated the traitors
with their far
superior strength.
Shampool was set free
within only three days.
[WOMAN 19A]
Mmwah!
[WALTER humming]
[YANG]
Good work today.
Judging by appearance,
the civilians gave you quite
the warm welcome, didn't they?
Ha! Well, the job's
gotta come with some perks.
Am I interrupting anything?
What brings everyone up here?
It turns out someone from
the Department of Intelligence
has fled to us from Heinessen
and is now requesting
an audience.
We're all here
awaiting his arrival.
Huh. From Intelligence?
Unrelated, I see Lieutenant
Greenhill is absent.
[YANG]
Hmm.
Looks like he's here.
[YANG]
Have there been any executions?
Not at the moment, no.
However, key officials
such as Chief Cubersly,
and Fleet Commander-in
Chief Bewcock have been detained
and subsequently
removed from power.
I see. And what's the status
of each of the fleets?
I'm glad we're getting
straight to it.
I came here specifically because
there's something I must
tell you regarding that.
The 11th Fleet has
joined the coup d'état.
Not only that,
I'm afraid to say,
it's heading straight for us.
I appreciate you
telling me about this.
If we're prepared for their
arrival, we can minimize losses.
Is that so?
Well, I'm happy to hear it, and
that I could be of some help.
Is something wrong?
Well... It's just that
I heard your adjutant
was Admiral
Greenhill's daughter,
yet I don't see her present.
She's well aware
of the position she's in.
So I've left her at Iserlohn.
[BAGHDASH] I see. I believe that
was a truly wise decision.
[WALTER]
Oh, damn it. Of course.
I just had to go and ruin
all these kiss marks.
Pardon me. Heh.
Now, then.
[FREDERICA] Yes. I have met
Commander Baghdash, in fact.
But it was only once.
In my father's study.
He was upset with the
current political system.
I remember him
openly complaining.
Well, that's good to know.
[RAINER]
The mission has been completed.
All right, good work.
Just keep a close eye
on the situation.
[RAINER]
Yes, sir.
Commodore. Where's
Commander Baghdash gone?
Oh, he's sleeping like a log.
I slipped him a
little something special.
It'll be a while before he
regains consciousness.
We can't be too careful with
a man who claims to be from
Intelligence and locking
him up may not be enough.
[YANG] Hmph. Guess so.
You certainly work fast.
[PATRICHEV] The 11th fleet
is heading this way,
and they're trying to trap us
in a pincer attack.
It looks like Commander
Baghdash's information
was correct after all.
He most likely wanted to
guarantee his own safety
above everything else.
[YANG] All right.
Thank you for the report.
[LEGRANGE] Any word
from Commander Baghdash?
[ADJUTANT 19A]
No, not yet sir.
[LEGRANGE sighs]
That useless fool.
Why infiltrate
their fleet, then?
Connect me to
all ships, immediately!
[LEGRANGE]
Attention, men.
The success of
this military revolution
and our homeland's destiny
depend on this battle.
Perform your duties
with every fragment
of your body and soul.
This is your gift
to the Republic.
I sincerely hope
I can count on your courage
and love for your homeland.
The time's come.
Give it your all!
[YANG yawns]
[FREDERICA]
Admiral.
Huh?
Aren't you going
to address the fleet?
Right.
Okay, everyone.
The battle is about to begin.
This is our fleet's
first campaign.
It's a meaningless fight,
which means losing would
be even more meaningless.
I've devised a way
for us to win.
So take it easy and
try not to push yourselves.
All that's riding on this...
...is the life or
death of a nation.
Compared to our individual
freedoms and rights,
a nation isn't worth much.
[TACTICAL OFFICER 13A]
Enemy fleet detected!
Twelve o'clock!
[YANG] All right, everyone,
I guess it's about time
to get started.
[NARRATOR] Thus, the battle
between the Yang Fleet
and the 11th Fleet began.
With the information
he obtained from Baghdash.
Yang used the enemy's
strategy against them,
focusing efforts on the main
fleet at their left flank.
This gave him the
advantage in numbers.
Our squadron is
the spearhead of this plan.
We're charging straight into the
heart of the enemy's ranks!
Fire! Fire everything
you've got!
[TACTICAL OFFICER 19A] We're
being attacked from 3 o'clock!
It's the Yang Fleet!
How did that man know
what we were going to do?
Could Baghdash have told him?
Contact the detached force
on our right flank!
Sir!
[TACTICAL OFFICER 19B] We're
being attacked from 11 o'clock!
The main fleet on the left flank
has encountered the enemy, too.
They believe that
it is Yang's squadron.
Commence counterattack!
[FISCHER] There's no need
to defeat the enemy.
We only need to slow them down
so they can't join
the main fleet.
This is great!
We don't even need to
waste time picking a target!
Keep firing until
there's nothing left!
[NGUYEN] We're gonna blast our
way right through their flank!
Charge! Charge!
The front and rear of our fleet
will be divided at this rate.
Pull it together!
Get our gunships
to the battle sector.
Do whatever it takes
to stop them!
[POPLIN] Our job's to keep
the enemy from regrouping.
Rum and Applejack are
on the squadron commander.
Sherry and Cognac,
you're with me.
[RUM, APPLEJACK, SHERRY, COGNAC]
Roger!
[ADJUTANT 19A] The rear
of our fleet was separated
from the line and
is taking fire!
[growls]
Turn around!
We're going back
to help the rear ships!
What's happening?!
[ATTENBOROUGH]
Keep these ships where they are
until the rear is taken care of.
They're obviously trying
to provide backup
and there's no reason
for us to let them.
Right.
[JULIAN gasps]
It's been two hours
since this started.
Their rear line is mostly
under our control, but--
It's taking more
than we thought.
We've advised them to surrender?
Indeed, we have.
They haven't responded yet.
I see...
[OFFICERS screaming]
[yelling]
The outcome's clearly decided,
yet they won't give in.
Come on... Hurry up
and surrender already.
The hell? Don't you guys
like booze and women?
There's too much to live for to
kill yourself over ideology!
Advise them to surrender again.
[COMMS. OFFICER 13C]
Transmission from the
11th Fleet flagship!
Connect us.
Admiral Legrange.
I, Legrange, have
taken the responsibility
of giving all ships in the 11th
fleet the order to surrender,
effective immediately.
I consider it an honor
to have fought this battle.
To think my final one would be
against such a renowned admiral.
However, though our fleet
may have been defeated
in battle, the military
council still lives on.
Our quest for salvation
shall prevail!
I wish to take this opportunity
to plead with you.
Reconsider the future
that you desire.
[gasps]
[LEGRANGE] To the
military council, we hail.
[gunshot]
[NARRATOR]
With Legrange's suicide,
the Battle of the Doria
Starzone came to an end.
The Yang fleet's goal was to
minimize losses on both sides,
but the opposition's faith
remained steadfast,
resulting in
a bitter conclusion.
[PATRICHEV]
Ever since Baghdash woke up,
he's been completely
insufferable.
He demands wine with
his meals and insists we have
a female soldier wait on him.
[ATTENBOROUGH]
Yeah.
But the admiral's seeing
him at the moment.
I'm sure he's setting
him straight as we speak.
Right, Lao?
Huh?
Uh... Right...
Go on...
Of course. To put it simply,
I was hoping you would allow me
to work for you from now on.
Is it really
that easy for a man
to completely change
his principles?
[BAGHDASH]
Absolutely.
Principles are nothing, but a
man's means of staying alive.
If they happen to
get in the way of that,
one need only get rid of them.
Is that so?
Could you tell me in more
detail what you had in mind?
First, I feel I should tell you
what my goal was
as a covert agent.
It was to assassinate you,
Admiral Yang.
I genuinely believed
this coup d'état had a chance
at being successful.
Which is why I was willing to
accept such a risky mission.
But... It's clear now
my judgement was wrong.
Your abilities far
surpassed my expectations,
as well as those of the National
Salvation Military Council.
And so, I've been
left with no other choice.
I'll accept the truth
of the situation.
No choice, huh?
That's the entire reason you
want to work for the opposition?
[BAGHDASH chuckles]
That's right.
If I'm being honest, I've grown
tired of idling my life away.
And I don't particularly
dislike working.
So won't you consider giving me
some kind of job to do?
Just anything?
All right, then. I'll surely
find a use for you eventually.
In the meantime,
you can have this back.
[gun clicking]
Admiral Yang.
[BAGHDASH]
Hmph.
[gasps]
Commander Baghdash.
Drop your weapon and put your
hands in the air now!
Whoa, whoa, whoa!
It was just a joke!
I owe Admiral Yang my life--
I'd never actually shoot him!
[JULIAN]
If you killed the admiral,
your name would
go down in history,
even if only in notoriety.
Can you truly say you didn't
feel that temptation, even once?
Kid... C'mon...
[JULIAN] Admiral! I don't
trust this man one bit!
He may swear
his loyalty to you now,
but there's no telling
what he'll do in the future!
The possibility of danger
is not a good reason
to take someone's
life, Julian. Okay?
I know that!
But...
Just let the guy off the hook.
You've scared him
enough already...
Commander?
Feel free to take your leave.
[BAGHDASH sighs]
If it helps, I'll try and
remember you'll always
be keeping an eye on me.
Not that you have any need to.
Please excuse me.
Admiral!
That Baghdash
is a very calculating guy.
As long as I keep winning,
he's not going to turn on me.
And for the time being,
that's good enough.
Besides... I don't want
to let you kill anyone
if I can avoid it.
[NARRATOR] Meanwhile, on
Heinessen, thousands of citizens
were assembling at
a stadium for a rally.
One to protest the National
Salvation Military Council.
[CROWD yelling]
[MAN 19A]
It's about to start!
Everything ready over there?
[MAN 19B]
We need a little more time!
We'll let you know as soon
as we hear something!
I can only hope that
this assembly is the beginning
of a new era for the Alliance,
Jean Robert.
[gasping]
[CHRISTIAN]
You...
Citizens clinging
to your arrogant ideals.
Have you gathered
here aware that
you are under martial law?
[laughs]
Hey. Pick ten of them
out from the crowd
and put them up on the stage.
[SOLDIER 19A]
Yes, Sir!
[MEN grunting]
[CHRISTIAN]
How about some answers?
You all must have a leader.
Is it Jessica Edwards?
Don't know.
Is that a fact?
Well, then...
Let me jog your memory!
[MAN A yells]
[PROTESTERS gasping]
[CHRISTIAN]
Goodness, what's wrong?
Are you not feeling well?
Perhaps you can help me.
Is Jessica Edwards...
--...your leader?!
--[JESSICA] Captain Christian!
[CHRISTIAN]
Speak of the devil.
Assemblywoman Edwards.
[JESSICA] Why have you brought
armed soldiers to interfere
with a peaceful assembly?
To restore order,
I would think it's obvious.
Take a look at yourselves.
Don't you think you're
the ones disturbing order
with your show of violence?
You struck a man.
Exactly what part of that
would you call "order"?
[CHRISTIAN chuckles]
We're the ones who decide
the definition of that word.
End this assembly at once.
If you don't understand
"order," we will be happy
to demonstrate it for you.
That's enough, Captain!
[CHRISTIAN grunts]
Ge-Get off!
[JESSICA yelps, grunts]
[CHRISTIAN] Not a single one
of you is even prepared to die,
yet you run your mouths to me?!
[JESSICA]
So if you're prepared to die...
...you can just do whatever
you want, no matter how stupid?
What?!
[JESSICA] History has
seen people like you...
People who used
violence to force
their ideas of
justice on others.
Most notably... was the
founder of the Galactic Empire:
Rudolf von Goldenbaum.
Then there's you...
At the bottom of that list.
You're just an unworthy
disciple to Rudolf.
[CHRISTIAN growls]
[JESSICA]
Reflect on that.
You have... no right
to be here now. So...
...take your soldiers and
leave this place immediately.
[CHRISTIAN]
Those... eyes...
Who the hell do
you think you are?!
[CHRISTIAN]
Hmph.
[CITIZEN 19A snalrs]
[PROTESTERS yelling]
[SOLDIER 19A]
Stop! Stop or we will shoot!
--I swear we'll do it!
--[screaming, shouting]
It doesn't matter! Just shoot!
--[gunshot]
--[CHRISTIAN grunts]
[SOLDIER 19C] One of them got
hold of a weapon somehow!
[SOLDIER 19D]
Sir... We can't handle this!
We have no choice!
Permission to fire!
Don't move!
Do it and I'll shoot!
[CITIZEN 19D]
Get him!
[CITIZENS grunting]
[NARRATOR] In this incident
which would later be known
as the Stadium Massacre,
20,000 civilians
and 1,500 soldiers
lost their lives.
All of whom
were fellow citizens
of the Free Planets Alliance.
[gasps]
I can't believe
he was so reckless.
And now... he may have
just driven all the citizens
to revolt at once.
Which means we would
lose our people's support.
We'd become a minority.
How can this be...?
[NARRATOR]
News of the Stadium Massacre
did not reach the
Hyperion instantly.
It was late by one month.
[YANG sighs]
Looks good.
You have permission to deliver
this notice to all ships.
I'll get right on that.
[NARRATOR] When he learned
of Jessica's death,
Yang decided to wear
sunglasses for the entire day
in order to hide his expression.
[NARRATOR] At the end of July,
in the year UC 797,
Yang's fleet was
approaching its destination,
and would soon
arrive at Heinessen.
[NARRATOR] Next time on
Legend of the Galactic Heroes:
Die Neue These: episode 20,
"Tragedy."