[NARRATOR] Under the command
of Reinhard von Lohengramm,
the Imperial Navy deflected
the Free Planets Alliance's
attempted invasion,
shifting to a major offensive.
After losing three of their
fleets, the Alliance chose
to relocate the battle to
the Amritsar Starzone.
[NARRATOR]
Most of their surviving fleets
sustained heavy losses.
But the 13th fleet,
under the command
of Vice Admiral Yang
Wen-li, made it out
with around 90% of
its fighting strength.
[BEWCOCK]
Per orders from headquarters,
we've laid a dense
minefield in our wake.
Thanks, that should
come in handy.
It will at least prevent
pincer attacks from the rear.
Our backs are pushed
against the wall.
Wish we weren't trapped.
No escape now, huh?
And yet, you seem
to be quite at ease.
By the way, am I correct in
assuming that the remaining
soldiers of the tenth fleet
are now under your command?
Yes. I'm getting good
at collecting survivors.
It's a curse. What'd I do
to deserve such a hard time?
You're starting to sound
like Yusuf the Complainer.
Most of the tenth's
fleet was damaged.
But those in fighting
shape will be useful.
If this plan is going to work,
we'll need every
ship we can get.
Admiral Ulanhu's
sacrifice was not in vain.
[YANG]
Hmm.
I'll see you in battle.
Until then.
[YANG]
Right.
Well, sir.
I should be getting
back to my own ship.
Attenborough.
I'm glad you're still alive.
Me, too. Plus, somebody's gotta
watch your back and make sure
you don't get yourself
killed out here.
[chuckles]
[ATTENBOROUGH]
I'm off.
Admiral.
We have received a report
from Commodore Fischer--
the mobilization plan
for the surviving fleets
has been completed.
Thank you.
That didn't take long.
And on a more personal note,
you should eat something
in this down time.
I'm afraid I don't
have much of an appetite.
I think I'll just have
a glass of brandy instead.
[FREDERICA]
Didn't Julian tell you
that you shouldn't
be drinking so much?
Hold on.
Are you two gonna
start ganging up on me?
[gasps]
We're just concerned!
--[alarm sounding]
--[gasping]
[TACTICAL OFFICER 13A]
Patrol craft 09 is detecting
an enemy fleet.
It's heading toward us
in tight formation.
Right, you all heard the alert.
All hands to battle
stations, condition one.
[TACTICAL OFFICER 13A]
Roger. All hands...
Listen, if we survive this,
I promise I'll eat healthy
for the rest of my life.
[OBERSTEIN] Reuenthal,
Mittermeyer and all other
admirals have now arrived in
their designated sectors.
Everyone is in place.
The enemy appears
to be organizing behind
some mined-out asteroids
that have been abandoned
since the days of
the Galactic Federation.
Is that why they
chose Amritsar
to be their battleground?
Likely so.
Fire now.
The enemy is focusing attacks
on the third and eighth fleets,
which are currently
the ships stationed closest
to the asteroid mines.
They'll pick them off
then move to our main formation.
All ships advance.
We'll attract their attention.
Get me Admiral Bewcock.
Yes, sir.
[TACTICAL OFFICER 13B]
Enemy approaching.
Rebels at 10 o'clock.
It's the flagship
of their fifth fleet,
the Rio Grande.
These damn kids.
Always pushing
their elders around.
[MITTERMEYER] All ships
change targets and strike
the rebels's fifth fleet.
[grunting]
[TACTICAL OFFICER 13B] We've
taken a hit to our right flank!
It's another enemy force!
[BEOWULF ADJUTANT 13A]
That's the 13th fleet.
They're moving in quickly.
They struck us
as we were preoccupied
with changing our targets.
How impressive.
It appears the enemy
has someone on their side
who excels in
fleet coordination.
Attention all ships,
pull back for now.
We'll regroup our forces.
[MURAI]
The enemy fleet is falling back.
Sometimes, having a smart
opponent works out for us.
[TACTICAL OFFICER 13A]
Search systems have identified
a new enemy fleet
approaching at 2 o'clock!
This battlefield has
hence been claimed
by the Schwarz Lanzenreiter!
Destroy the rebel scum!
[OBERSTEIN] Our navy
is currently overwhelming
the rebels in all theaters,
your excellency.
Victory appears inevitable.
[YANG sighs]
Looks like we've lost.
Our prey is none other
than that infamous rebel,
Yang Wen-li, and his fleet.
His defeat shall net us
whatever reward we desire!
Keep pushing forward!
The goddess of victory, Nike, is
flashing her damn panties at us!
Admiral. Here they come!
Increase shields to max output.
Attack while withdrawing in
sync with the enemy's advance.
[YANG]
Adjust our retreat speed.
Bait their commanders.
Fly slow enough that
they think they've got us.
[EUGEN] The enemy is maintaining
a well-calculated distance.
We've dealt almost
no damage at all.
All ships cease fire.
Deploy every Walküres now!
This sector shall be ours!
[TACTICAL OFFICER 13A]
Carrier-based crafts
coming in fast!
Your orders, sir?
Maintain course.
We need to draw them in closer.
[TACTICAL OFFICER 13A]
They're right on top of us!
Set destroyers
to focus on defense.
Have our capital ships divert
all power from the shields
to the cannons.
Isn't your suggestion
putting us in danger?
Don't you worry.
Fire!
What are you fools doing?!
Use our ship's guns
to take them out!
We can't, sir!
Why not?!
The Walküres
are in the line of fire,
we'd end up hitting our own men.
They must have realized
we can't counterattack.
[BITTENFELD growls]
[COMMS. OFFICER 13A]
Incoming message from
Admiral Bittenfeld.
"Immediate backup requested."
He wants reinforcements?
Does he think I'm some sort
of wizard who can conjure
new fleets into existence
with nothing more
than a flick of the wrist?!
Message the Bittenfeld Fleet.
I have no forces to spare.
Continue to fight.
And win with the soldiers
you already have.
[COMMS. OFFICER 13A]
Yes, sir.
[REINHARD]
Has Kircheis arrived yet?
Are you concerned,
Your Excellency?
Of course not,
I'm simply curious.
[OBERSTEIN] I'd wager Admiral
Kircheis has already navigated
the special ops
craft into position.
It's likely he's begun
the operation by now.
[TACTICAL OFFICER 13C]
The Seffle particles have
successfully penetrated
the enemy's minefield.
Ignite immediately.
[TACTICAL OFFICER 13D] Enemy
fleet of approximately 30,000
approaching from the rear.
[BEWCOCK]
How'd the Imperials manage
to break through our mines?!
[YANG] An ambush led by
that tactician in the red ship.
To be honest, I was wondering
when he would show up.
So how would you like
us to proceed, Admiral?
Well, let's see...
We'll make a run for it, with as
many allies as we possibly can.
I'll do my best to
protect their ships.
[TACTICAL OFFICER 13E]
Reuenthal's Fleet is performing
search-and-destroy operations
on the enemy's ninth.
Meanwhile, the Mittermeyer Fleet
has prevented the enemy
from organizing in the area.
Order to all fleets.
Switch from pincer
formation to encirclement.
Let none of those
rebel soldiers escape.
Shall we bring
the flapship forward?
What do you think?
No, we'll stay
right where we are.
I wouldn't want
my soldiers to think
I was stealing their glory.
It seems that
the Bittenfeld Fleet
has lost too many
of their ranks.
[REINHARD]
Tch.
[OBERSTEIN]
If we don't complete the circle,
we'll be providing
the enemy an escape route.
Unlike earlier when the
request for backup came in,
we now have extra
forces available.
Someone needs to reinforce
Admiral Bittenfeld,
and as quickly as possible
Damn thorn in my side.
Once again that bastard's
ineptitude ruins things for us.
[COMMS. OFFICER 13B]
Message from command.
Admiral Kircheis is
to provide backup
to the Schwarz
Lanzenreiter immediately.
[COMMS. OFFICER 13C]
The enemy fleet behind us
has deployed to
our left flank!
They're trying to fill
the gap in their encirclement.
[COMMS. OFFICER 13C]
Urgent encrypted transmission
from Commodore Attenborough.
Sorry to keep you all waiting.
We're ready to start the plan.
[YANG]
Hmm. Then begin immediately.
[TACTICAL OFFICER 13F]
Part of the rebel fleet
is moving towards
our right flank!
Don't let them past us!
Expand the encirclement
to our right!
[gasps]
No, don't!
Proceed as planned.
Begin Stage Two.
[COMMS. OFFICER 13D]
Message from Admiral Kircheis.
[BITTENFELD grunts]
[COMMS. OFFICER 13D]
"The enemies to the right
are a diversion.
Maintain formation
until my fleet arrives."
What?
[TACTICAL OFFICER 13F] Enemy
approaching from the front.
[BITTENFELD growls]
I don't understand this!
[TACTICAL OFFICER 13F] The
mined-out asteroids are headed
straight for us as high speeds!
That's impossible!
I've done all I can do--
now it's up to you.
--[BITTENFELD gasps]
--[EUGEN] Our circle...
[YANG] Focus on
the enemy in front of us.
Hit those black ships
with everything we've got
and clear a path for our fleets.
[EUGEN] We've lost over
70% of our vessels!
Thirty percent still remain!
But Admiral...
We will lay down our lives
to stop the rebels!
Even if every last man falls!
We mustn't!
Our fleet has become
the weak link
in the encirclement, Admiral.
We have to pull back immediately
and report our current status
to the commander-in-chief.
Or would you allow the legacy of
Schwarz Lanzenreiter to
die here on this battlefield?
[BITTENFELD growls]
[NARRATOR] The second
major battle of the invasion,
which took place in
the Amritsar star zone,
ended in what seemed to be
an overwhelming advantage
for the Imperial Navy.
However, due to the efforts of
the Alliance commanders,
particularly Yang,
the Empire failed to
complete their encirclement.
This allowed the
surviving Alliance
fleets to escape--though just
barely--from certain defeat.
[MITTERMEYER] The rebels
must have impressive men
in their ranks.
Though we do as well.
Yes. I look forward
to meeting them again.
Although... I doubt that will
happen for quite a while.
I think you're right.
They've lost both
strength and will.
They won't attempt another
invasion any time soon.
I wish I could say
that you displayed
a shred of heroism.
But I cannot.
Yes, sir!
You must know why.
In your quest for glory,
you rushed headfirst
into battle recklessly.
As a result, your fleet
suffered heavy losses,
and the rebels escaped because
our encirclement was incomplete.
Do you object
to anything I've said?
I don't, sir...
We uphold a system of
reward and punishment here.
Once we return to Odin, I'll
ensure you're held accountable
for your actions.
You're confined to
your quarters for now.
Dismissed.
[BITTENFELD whimpers]
[OBERSTEIN] You are a capable
man, but you shouldn't assume
your friendship with
Count Lohengramm
will allow you
any kind of privilege.
[OBERSTEIN] A wise ruler
does not let personal feelings
influence his decisions.
[KIRCHEIS] Your Excellency.
Please reconsider this.
Why do you want to stop me?!
Bittenfeld obviously
failed to fulfill his duty!
It's only natural
that he be punished.
Your Excellency...
Are you angry right now?
[REINHARD]
What of it if I am?!
And what is it that
you're angry about?
Is it Bittenfeld's failures?
Because I don't
believe that, Excellency.
Stop calling me that.
What do you want to say?
Just spit it out.
Fine, then.
If that's what you wish.
Is it possible that, deep down,
the person you're actually
mad at is yourself?
Because I honestly believe that
Admiral Bittenfeld is merely
a victim of your own
misplaced anger, Reinhard.
You've assured
Admiral Yang's reputation.
And you're this upset over it?
[REINHARD snarls]
Damn right I'm upset!
I managed to endure it
back at Astarte,
but now he's bested
me twice in a row!
Every time...
Why does that man always
show up to thwart me when
I'm on the verge of
complete victory?!
He more than likely
has his own complaints.
In fact, I'm certain of it.
It must frustrate him that he
can't face you on equal footing
from the beginning
Remember, you are
fighting on two fronts.
Admiral Yang in front of you,
and the high nobles behind you.
We must be cautious
of those surrounding us.
So please, Reinhard...
Don't make enemies out of
your own subordinates as well.
All right, then.
I was mistaken.
I won't have
Bittenfeld punished.
Would you please
relay that to him?
I can't be the one
to do that for you.
[REINHARD] You're right,
it's meaningless if
it doesn't come from me.
Tell me, Kircheis.
Yes, what is it, Reinhard?
Do you believe I can seize
this universe as my own?
If you are not capable
of that feat, no one is.
Go forth and make it yours.
[footsteps approaching]
S'all right, I'm just resting--
forgive my appearance.
Yes, sir. Would you
like some tea?
[YANG] Sure, with plenty of
brandy in it, if you please.
Right.
[YANG]
Sub-lieutenant.
Huh?
[YANG] I've studied
a fair amount of history.
And one thing I've learned is
that in every human society,
there are two main
schools of thought.
There are those who believe
there exists something
more valuable than a life.
And those who believe that
nothing is more important.
When people go to war,
they use the former
as an excuse,
and when they stop fighting,
they give the latter
as the reason.
This has been true
for hundreds--
no, thousands of years.
I wonder...
Will that continue to be the
case for a thousand more?
I'm not sure...
[YANG] No, nevermind--
humanity as a whole.
The real question is...
Can I do anything to justify
all the blood I've spilled?
Was it worth it?
[YANG] Uh. I'm sorry, that was
weird to say, d-disregard that.
Oh, please,
it's perfectly all right.
If you'll excuse me, I'll go get
that tea and a bit of brandy.
Lots of it.
[FREDERICA]
Yes. Lots of it.
[NARRATOR]
Accepting responsibility
for the worst defeat in history,
the entire Alliance High
Council resigned.
When Job Trunicht,
one of the members who voted
in opposition to the invasion,
left his position
as National Defense Committee
Chairman, he was immediately
appointed as the head
of the interim government.
[NARRATOR]
In the military division,
Fleet Admiral Sithole, the
Integrated Tactical Operations
Center Chief,
and Fleet Admiral Lobos,
the Space Fleet supreme
commander both resigned.
Admiral Dwight Greenhill
was relegated
to inspector general of the
National Defense Committee
General Secretariat and
was then removed from
the military's front line.
[NARRATOR]
Rear Admiral Alex Caselnes,
who took responsibility for
the supply line failure,
was sent far away
from Heinessen,
to the frontier lands.
Unfortunately, this move took
him a great distance away
from his family.
Former operations staff
officer Commodore Falk
was reassigned to reserve
duty after medical treatment.
The First Fleet
commander, Kubersly,
became the new Operations
Center Chief, and Bewcock,
after a promotion to Admiral,
was named the new Space
Fleet Commander-in-Chief
[NARRATOR] There was
much discussion as to what
to do with Yang, and
a final decision was not made
until he returned from his
requested three-week vacation.
He was promoted to
Iserlohn Fortress commander
and garrison commander.
On top of that, he received
a promotion to Admiral.
His first orders were
to immediately relocate
to Iserlohn Fortress.
[NARRATOR] There he'd be
joined by his adjutant,
Lieutenant Frederica Greenhill,
garrison vice commander,
Rear Admiral Edwin Fischer,
Fortress Defense Commander
Commodore Walter von Schönkopf,
chief of staff,
Rear Admiral Murai.
vice chief of staff,
Commodore Fyodor Patrichev,
division commander,
Rear Admiral Dusty Attenborough,
Rear Admiral Nguyen Van Huu,
staff officer, Commander Lao,
first Fortress Space
Squadron captain,
Lieutenant Commander
Olivier Po-plin,
second Fortress
Space Squadron captain,
Lieutenant Commander Ivan
Konev, and Julian Mintz,
who joined the military
as a paid civilian.
[NARRATOR] As the new Yang fleet
came together to take control
of Iserlohn Fortress,
the fortress commander's
main concern was the
movement of the Imperial Navy.
Now that the Alliance Navy
was in a weakened state,
he feared their enemies
might go on the offensive.
[NARRATOR] However, his
worries were unnecessary...
[NARRATOR]
...due to the unexpected death
of Kaiser Friedrich the fourth.
[NARRATOR] Next time, on
Legend of the Galactic Heroes:
Die Neue These: Episode 14,
"Demise of the Emperor."