According to the agenda,
you have a lunch meeting
scheduled with Chairman Trunicht
at 11 o'clock.
Duly noted.
[FALK]
Chief Cubersly!
Commodore Falk. Good to see you.
It's my understanding you took
a medical leave of absence.
I've fully recovered.
I'm back to myself.
And with your help I'd like to
make my return to active duty.
Your reinstatement?
And your doctor
already approved this?
Well, of course he already has,
that's why I'm here.
He endorsed me without concern.
I see.
Then I suggest you
follow regulations.
Just submit a formal request
and your doctor's note
to the defense committee.
As you know,
they need to authorize it.
Going through official
channels is the--
Yes, but doing all of
that will take far too long.
I'm ready to start today
and be of service again
to our great nation.
I'd trust you to remember
that standard procedures
always take some time
to process, Commodore.
Which is exactly why I hoped
that you could help me.
[CUBERSLY] I'm afraid
you've misunderstood me.
[FALK]
Ah...
Allow me to clarify.
My job is to see that
protocol is followed.
Not broken,
as you wish to believe.
You seem to think
you're entitled
to some sort of
special treatment.
But in my opinion,
it appears you're still in need
of more rehabilitation.
And in your current state,
your lack of cooperation
would only promote confusion.
That would be bad for you,
and certainly for everyone else.
Give it some time.
That's my advice.
Pardon, sir, but we
should get going now.
Of course. Good day, then.
Heh...
[WHITTY]
Watch out!
[CUBERSLY gasps]
[screams]
Raugh!
[FALK grunts]
[WHITTY]
Man down!
Call a doctor! Hurry it up!
[chuckles]
[NARRATOR] Reserve Commodore
Falk's assassination attempt
against Operations
Center Chief Cubersly was
an unprecedented incident
of internal violence
towards a key military figure.
[NARRATOR] In the aftermath
of the failed invasion
of the Empire, the people's
despair deepened,
and the disorder
fueled national tensions
to an unbearable extreme.
They want me
to act as interim chief
while also serving
my current position?
[PFEIFER]
Yes, sir.
It was a confidential request
from the Defense Committee.
Then you can
tell them I decline.
That's a recklessly
problematic solution.
Delegating both Operations
Center and Commander-in-Chief
duties to one person is foolish.
We should be avoiding
risks, not taking them.
[NARRATOR] Given the
commotion, many had thought
that selecting a provisional
successor would be difficult.
But one man volunteered
himself for the role.
An officer of meager
popularity at best,
Admiral Dawson.
[BEWCOCK]
On second thought,
maybe I should've
said yes after all. [sighs]
[NARRATOR]
Unfortunately, tragedy struck
the very next day.
[NARRATOR] An accidental
explosion resulted in fire
at the maintenance center
of the Air Defense Base.
There were 14 casualties.
All of them young soldiers
who had yet to reach
the age of 20.
Naturally, this horrified
Alliance citizens.
[JESSICA] This brutal war
with the Galactic Empire
has dragged on for
over 150 years.
And all for what?
Sacrificing countless
children to fuel
an endless conflict?
Do we want to live in a
society that would accept this
as normal?
Now's the time
to question everything
we've been told was true.
That there was no other way
to stop this bloodshed.
There's only one solution.
And it is peace!
She definitely doesn't
hold anything back.
[BEWCOCK] She shouldn't.
Because she's absolutely right.
There's something
very wrong with a civilization
that would let an old soldier
such as myself live on
while the young ones die.
If no one calls
attention to that,
then things will only
continue to get worse.
We need to protect
hearts and minds like hers.
Without them, the Alliance
would surely lose its humanity.
[DAWSON]
As I'm sure you've been aware.
For the last two weeks
we've been seeing a series
of violent revolutions breaking
out on the planets Neptis,
Kaffa, Purmurend, and Shampool.
--[YANG] Right.
--Your orders are to lead
the Iserlohn Garrison Fleet
and put an end to
any resistance efforts
as quickly as possible
to restore balance.
This is all happening
on four different planets.
We'd be leaving the fortress
vulnerable for quite
a hefty length of time.
The Empire is
currently preoccupied with
a vast civil war.
There's very little chance of
them invading Iserlohn
with anything approaching
considerable numbers.
I'm certain
you'll be able to fulfill
your soldierly duty
without reservations,
Commander Yang.
[JULIAN]
What's this Dawson's deal?
How old is he?
[YANG]
I'd say he's in his mid 40s.
I suppose his most immediate
goal as my superior
is to work us as hard
as he possibly can.
Though I haven't
the faintest clue as to why.
He has a reputation for holding
personal grudges but I've never
met the man, so I don't see
any reason for him to resent me.
If I'm not mistaken,
you'll be turning 30
this year, right, sir?
Yeah. I guess
I've hit that age, huh?
[JULIAN]
Well, that's why.
[YANG]
Hmm?
[JULIAN] You're so much
younger than he is.
But you're already
the same rank.
It's not like you're someone
old like Admiral Bewcock.
Of course he's jealous.
No kidding. That's funny.
I didn't even think of that.
Perhaps the admiral
wasn't able to predict
the assassination attempt,
but he did catch on
to what Lohengramm was planning.
The Marquis intends
to meddle with the Alliance
as much as he can
while keeping his hands clean.
He's intense.
I wonder what's next.
A takeover in the capital.
[YANG] But what's after
that is beyond me.
I doubt Marquis Lohengramm
actually knows, either.
Who's the mastermind
behind the coup?
That's the big question.
Do you have any ideas?
No clue. We'll
find out soon enough.
He's asking us
to stop rebellions
on four different planets, then?
All by ourselves?
[WALTER] So we're the ones
who have to sweat
while they get to keep their
forces sitting at home.
That's awfully petty.
[MURAI] Whatever the case may
be, we cannot refuse
any official orders from
Integrated Tactical Operations.
[TACTICAL OFFICER 13A]
Emergency in the capital!
Give us a detailed report.
Sir.
A state of emergency has been
declared on planet Heinessen.
It's-- It's a coup d'état!
[gasping]
As of this current day
of April 13th, UC 797.
For the sake of this nation,
we establish the National
Salvation Military Council
as the new government.
Heinessen is
now under martial law,
and our forces shall hereby
assume complete control
over the entire capital.
All in the name
of salvation, huh?
[BRONZE] The constitution
is dead and in its place
we implement the
following new decrees.
Your full attention, please.
Number one: A unified
national regime
will be forged with the
noble goal of vanquishing
the Galactic Empire.
Second: Political
activity and speech
contradicting the national
interest will be regulated.
Third: Military personnel
are granted
both judicial and police powers.
Fourth: Non-essential
social services will be cut
as to prevent the
weakening of society.
Fifth...
Well, isn't this flashy.
Sound familiar?
It's no different from what
Rudolf von Goldenbaum said
just over 500 years ago.
[BRONZE] And finally, for
the soldiers and citizens
of the Alliance,
the chairman of
the National Salvation
Military Council.
[BRONZE]
Admiral Dwight Greenhill.
--[rapid gunfire]
--[alarms blaring]
[GREENHILL] Attention.
Citizens and Soldiers alike.
There is no need to be
frightened by our actions.
Our goal is
to create a new world.
One in which all people may
enjoy a righteous reputation.
And live righteously
until our final days.
As it should be.
If you examine history,
you will see that when
government becomes fraudulent
and society loses its way,
there will always be those
who rise above the system
to rectify order.
We are the ones
who will inspire.
Revolution is here.
From this moment on,
the history of the Free Planets
Alliance shall change.
I must be going
senile in my old age.
Please forgive us, sir.
This is for the greater good.
I see you've all
been contaminated.
Not only the Departments of
Intelligence and Inspection,
but even the men who've been
serving directly under me.
[BEWCOCK]
Well, look who it is.
I recognize that stench.
You're Rear Admiral Lynch.
I'm so honored
that you remember me--
you're making me blush.
There was a time
I thought highly of you.
You were one of the most
sensible, reasonable men
in the service.
Sadly, it appears I
overestimated your character.
I never thought that
you would take part
in such an ugly affair.
I can only imagine that your
morality has fallen fast asleep.
Quite the opposite.
It feels like
I finally woke up.
Our government has become
crooked beyond function,
and the progression of
society has grown stagnant.
Mob rule is running rampant
in the guise of democracy.
And it shows no sign
of self-control.
How else are we supposed
to correct this behavior?
This is the path of reform.
So that's it.
I can agree with you that the
present system is certainly
stifled and corrupt.
However, I fail to
understand your solution
to overthrow
everything by force.
So, if I may venture to ask,
once you and your
military inevitably rot,
who corrects you? And how?
We had no other choice
but to take a stand.
And unlike those who
merely cry out for peace,
we intended to make it happen.
Evil is born from self-interest.
We will never
give into hypocrisy!
[BEWCOCK]
Hmph. Interesting.
It seems to me as though
you're simply justifying
a violent coup.
Dressing it up with passionate
words such as "salvation"
and other nonsense.
Admiral Bewcock.
I promise we have every
intention of behaving
as gentlemanly and
courteous as possible.
[BEWCOCK chuckles]
How very naïve.
Ever since the first humans
walked upon the earth,
governing the people with
acts of terrorism has never
been "civilized" and
certainly not "courteous."
If you want
people to call it that,
why not employ this
power you've gained?
You should try using it
to write a new dictionary
before you completely lose it.
[growling]
[GREENHILL] Unfortunately,
we can spend all day
speaking to each other,
but it's unlikely
we'll find any common ground.
The only choice left is to let
history itself be our judge.
Now take him to another room.
And remember to be respectful.
History may have nothing
to say about you, Admiral.
Keep that in mind.
[NARRATOR] The Alliance
capital of Heinessen was seized
by the military in a coup d'état
[NARRATOR]
Even Admiral Dawson,
interim chief of the Integrated
Tactical Operations Center,
was detained.
However, High Council
Chairman Trunicht,
the prime target of the attack,
was missing from his residence.
He was nowhere to be found.
[YANG] Looks like
you're hanging in there.
Is there something
I can do for you, commander?
I'm moving my fleet soon.
Will you join me?
Are you... really sure?
I just assumed,
considering the situation,
that I'd be relieved
immediately of my position
as your adjutant.
Do you want to quit?
[FREDERICA]
N-No! But...
[YANG] You know,
I'm an incompetent man.
I need someone
capable at my side.
[gasps]
I'd be lost without you.
Heh!
[whimpers]
Ah!
[FREDERICA]
Then...
...I promise...
I will do my best
to fulfill the role.
Thank you, sir.
So I take it
you decided not to
fire Miss Greenhill, then?
[YANG]
Hmph. Of course not.
Not until I can replace her with
someone who's as talented
as she is, anyway.
[WALTER chuckles]
You could just be honest.
About what, exactly?
Oh, well, you know.
I was simply contemplating
the way she feels about you.
And how might you feel about me?
Hard to say.
Frankly, I'm not entirely sure
what to think of you quite yet.
To put it another way,
you're a walking contradiction.
[WALTER] No one despises
the foolishness of war
as much as you do.
And yet, there's no greater
master of it than yourself.
Am I wrong?
[YANG sighs]
I appreciate the sentiment,
but what about Reinhard
von Lohengramm?
Watching you face off
would be fascinating.
Personally speaking, if you
both mobilized your forces
under equal conditions,
I'm confident that you
would defeat him.
That doesn't amount
to more than wishful thinking.
[WALTER] Hmph. At any rate,
let's move on to the next topic.
You possess a profoundly
intimate knowledge
of the Free Planets Alliance's
current power structure,
and understand too well
how corrupt it happens to be.
Yet you persevere,
devoting all of your efforts
into trying to save it.
Why, that's another
glaring contradiction.
The truth is,
"best" doesn't exist,
but "better" does.
I recognize that
the Alliance hasn't
always played nice.
But the National Salvation
Military Council...
You heard their credo.
Without a doubt,
they are infinitely worse
than the present regime.
[YANG grunting]
If I might be so brazen,
I believe we should let those
buffoons in the military council
purge away the
prevailing officials.
Thoroughly. And permanently.
In due time, they'll expose
their incompetence as leaders.
That's when you
make your entrance.
You'll chase out
the last hypocrites.
And seize control as
the man who restored democracy.
Now that would be "better."
How about it?
You can have whatever
title you want.
Become a leader with the
power to protect the people,
however you see fit!
[YANG]
Yang Wen-li the Dictator, huh?
Sorry, but I don't really
think that's my style
[WALTER sighs]
[WALTER]
You know,
playing soldier doesn't seem
to suit you much either.
And despite that,
you're doing
remarkably well at it.
If you put your mind to it,
I wager you'd make
a pretty good dictator.
[YANG]
Commodore Schönkopf?
[WALTER]
Yes?
Regarding these thoughts
you've mentioned,
have you shared your ideas
with anyone besides me?
Ah. I would never.
Very well, then.
[GREENHILL] Yang Wen-li has
formally refused to participate
in the Council's efforts.
Admiral Legrange.
Sir.
[GREENHILL] You will lead the
Eleventh Fleet in the battle
against Yang's forces.
Do not hold back.
Mission accepted.
Wait. But then, what
about your daughter?
Unfortunate as it may be,
for our plan to succeed,
I had to gave up on her.
I understand, sir.
You have my word that
I'll make them submit to us.
Or annihilate them
completely, if necessary.
What a surprise.
I never realized
your true calling was
as a grand spokesperson.
Maybe. But I
really wasn't bluffing
when said those things.
It was the truth.
[CLERK 17A]
You there.
You live with Admiral
Yang. Is that right?
[JULIAN]
Yes?
[CLERK 17A]
What's your take?
Do you think he has any
chance of winning this thing?
[ONLOOKERS murmuring]
You should know Admiral
Yang Wen-li doesn't fight
any battles he can't win.
--[ONLOOKERS gasping]
--What the...
--Hear that? He's right!
--Yep. That's Yang! Heh!
We'll be fine!
You're Miracle Yang, after all
[YANG]
Talk to me about the boy.
Is he ready to ship out?
How's his marksmanship
and hand-to-hand combat?
Speaking honestly
as his instructor,
he's more than sufficiently
prepared to stand as a soldier.
I imagine he will be of greater
use than you in that regard.
Heh!
Although... you ultimately want
more for Julian, don't you?
Something far beyond
the confines of all this.
There's limits to
our abilities as humans.
Despite that,
we have the means to set destiny
in motion with our choices.
My hope is that he accomplishes
that in as many ways as he can.
And even if he doesn't,
I still want him to have the
potential and skillset to do so.
Well? How 'bout yourself?
I'm afraid it's too late for me.
I've got myself chin-deep
to the point of no return
with the Alliance.
Nothing but obligations
to meet for the people
who pay my salary.
I understand.
Y'know, I'm beginning to see the
reason why you won't allow
Julian to become
official military.
You'd like to save him from
any compulsory obedience
to the Free Planets Alliance.
I'm not sure I'd given
it all that much thought.
[FREDERICA]
Admiral.
All ships have completed
preparations for departure.
Roger that.
What destination
would you like us
to set a course for, sir?
Okay, let's take a look.
[YANG]
Our final stop: Heinessen.
[NARRATOR]
On April 20th,
Yang appointed Caselnes
as the Interim Commander
of Iserlohn Fortress,
ordering all ships in
the adjacent garrison
fleet to mobilize.
[NARRATOR]
At this moment,
the future of the Free Planets
Alliance hung in the balance,
depending heavily upon
the Yang Fleet's next move.
[NARRATOR] Next time on
Legend of the Galactic Heroes:
Die Neue These: episode 18:
"Bloodshed in Space."