[HANS] We've been awaiting
your arrival, Milady.
There you are!
It's quite a relief to see
that you've made back safely.
Though. What led you to
return home in such haste?
Is everything all right, Madam?
Do tell me, Hans,
how has my father been doing?
[HILDA]
Hello, Father.
[FRANZ]
Oh, Hilda, it's you.
I thought I'd come to visit.
How nice.
Well then.
How are classes going?
Good as usual.
But I'm more interested
in learning about
what's keeping
you in deep thought.
Oh, nothing of
great importance, my dear.
[HILDA]
My, that's certainly reassuring.
So, the future
of the Mariendorf family
and the fate of the
Galactic Empire.
You say they're "nothing
of great importance?"
Whether you want to or not,
that's all you can hear about
when you live on Odin.
You're not the only
nobleman in a quandary
over who you'll
pledge allegiance to.
[FRANZ]
I see.
That being said,
have you arrived
at a decision yet?
[FRANZ] I would much
prefer to remain neutral.
But, if I absolutely must
choose a faction to advocate,
then yes.
We shall defer to
supporting Duke Braunschweig.
As imperial nobility,
the best option--
[HILDA]
Oh, Father.
[HILDA] There's a truth that
nearly all of the aristocracy
refuses to acknowledge.
Just as all people born
will eventually die,
all nations face
inevitable death as well.
Since the dawn of
human civilization on Earth.
Without a single outlier.
Ultimate destruction
always awaits us.
[HILDA]
So then, why?
Why should the Goldenbaum
Dynasty be the only exception
over any other age?
Hilda. Watch your tongue!
The Goldenbaum Dynasty
has already survived
for nearly 500 years now.
What's more, they did
this while oppressing
the population through
a depraved monopoly.
All of it was born out of a
desire for wealth and power.
Many people were killed.
Countless young daughters
were stolen away.
A multitude of manipulative laws
all made for exclusive benefit.
Tell me. Would it
really be all that surprising
if a nation like that were
on the verge of collapse?
Yes. Perhaps that may be.
But there's still no reason
for us to throw in
with Marquis Lohengramm.
[HILDA]
Oh, there is.
Very well.
My dear, I shall leave
it all in your hands.
[HILDA chuckles]
Thank you so much, Father,
for everything you've done.
You've given me
such a charmed life.
Right at the verge of
this most exciting era.
[RÜCKE]
My apologies for the wait!
His Excellency will see you now.
Right this way, madam.
[REINHARD] If only Kircheis
were here. What a shame.
He has a bit of history with
the Mariendorf household.
Are you familiar?
Yes, Of course.
We've never met but he
saved my father's life last year
during the Castrop rebellion.
So, what business
did you come to discuss?
I'm here as
a gesture of support, sir.
We, of the Mariendorf family,
would like to pledge
our solidarity to you
in the coming civil war.
What civil war?
[HILDA] The one brewing
against Duke Braunschwieg,
which could start at any moment.
[REINHARD] Hmph.
You're a bold one, aren't you?
Suppose what you say were true.
My victory would
hardly be guaranteed.
You still wish to
assert an alliance?
Yes. Because
I believe you'd win.
[REINHARD] Oh? And what
inspires this confidence?
[HILDA]
If you'll indulge me, sir.
First of all,
you have the blessing
of both the new Kaiser
and Marquis Lichtenlade.
Therefore, you possess
the just cause of subjugating
any opposition who
dare defy their authority.
On the other hand,
Duke Braunschweig
and Marquis Littenheim?
The two of them are waging
a selfish war as a means
of achieving nothing
but wealth and glory.
To that end,
they may have decided
to join forces temporarily.
But they have no the
desire to help each other.
Unlike the forces
of Marquis Lohengramm,
they lack both a solid chain
of command and a unified will.
Lastly, he may
not have been born
into a noble family
of high standing,
but neither were the rank
and file, ordinary soldiers
who fight for him.
This makes the Marquis quite
popular among the commoners.
The grassroots
support from the oppressed
will surely bring him victory.
I trust in you, Your Excellency.
To do away with
antiquated values.
And to build
a magnificent future
through this inevitable war.
How interesting.
I could use an insightful
and well-spoken ally
such as yourself.
I'll be certain to ensure
that the arrangement
is mutually beneficial.
Your family will be held
in favorable regard, of course.
And I shall extend that to any
other families you suggest.
I'm touched
by your generosity, sir.
Your words will doubtlessly
assuage my loved ones
to feel the same.
Please.
You went through the trouble
of coming to meet with me.
This is the least I can do to
compensate for your courage
and your thoughtfulness.
If there's anything
I can assist you with,
don't hesitate to ask me.
Whatever the request may be.
Well, as long
as you'll permit me,
then there is a favor
I'd like to invoke.
[REINHARD]
Go ahead.
[HILDA] If possible, I'd like to
request an official document
recognizing our fealty,
a token of our loyalty.
Something securing both
the house of Mariendorf's
social standings
and land rights.
Oh? Documentation?
Yes.
Very well.
I'll have that in writing for
you by the end of the day.
I'm incredibly grateful.
From this day forward,
I swear absolute devotion
on behalf of my family.
If I may, Fräulein Mariendorf.
Regarding the other
households you intend
to recruit on our behalf.
Will they require
similar documentation?
I would appreciate if
Your Excellency provided it
for those who so desire.
I'd wage those nobles
who don't request them have
no real need for such papers.
[REINHARD chuckles]
Yes, that's only fair.
I believe you
possess the ability
to recognize those worthy.
The people with the strength
to live in this coming age.
Oh? Then that's what I shall do.
I must say, Fräulein, you're
quite the clever young woman.
I never knew there were
people of nobility like you.
--[HILDA chuckles]
--[knocking]
[REINHARD]
You may enter.
Pardon me.
We have finally
received the report.
It's here.
This has been
a pleasure, Fräulein.
Please excuse me.
I hope we meet again.
Yes.
[sighs]
[NARRATOR] Meanwhile,
a gathering was held
on a private villa.
The noblemen against the
Lohengramm-Lichtenlade axis
formed an alliance.
It would become known
as the Lippstadt Pact.
It's leader:
Duke Otto von Braunschweig.
His second:
Marquis Wilhelm von Littenheim.
The number of participating
nobles totaled roughly 3,740.
And their soldiers
outnumbered Reinhard's forces.
[NARRATOR] They decided on a
name for their new organization.
The Lippstadt Nobles Coalition.
[BRAUNSCHWEIG]
Why the long face?
[OVLESSER]
Hm.
It doesn't suit you.
[horse whinnies]
[MÜCKENBERGER]
No need to salute me. Heh.
Not when I've left my position.
All right.
I've come to inform you
of a gathering being held
at Duke Braunschweig's villa.
Officially, it's billed
as a garden party.
Though I'm sure you can
imagine the true purpose.
Whatever it may be, I decline.
But Your Excellency!
I said to drop the formalities.
Are you still unable to
comprehend the boy's talent?
After everything,
why do you still take his side?
To put it simply,
it's because I can
see the truth.
[OVLESSER]
But, sir!
As a free civilian
in retirement.
Allow me to give you a piece
of important advice.
That boy intends to
defeat anyone who doubts him.
He will eradicate all who
are stuck in the past.
[OVLESSER growls]
[FLEGEL] How dare he
make a mockery of us.
The nerve of that man!
Muckenberger
is getting on in years.
Let this be a reminder that
you shouldn't act on your own!
Besides, as coalition leader,
I shall command the frontlines--
[LITTENHEIM] Sir. I don't
believe it's strategically sound
to deploy yourself out there.
No, that would
expose you, Commander.
Perhaps we should designate
a tactical specialist.
[BRAUNSCHWEIG growls]
[BRAUNSCHWEIG]
Admiral Merkatz.
Please, take a seat.
[MERKATZ] You may ask
as many times as you like,
but my answer hasn't changed.
A struggle like this will
do more harm than good.
Please reconsider engaging
in such a venture.
You're mistaken.
This endeavor is a righteous
crusade to protect
the sovereignty of the
great Goldenbaum Dynasty.
Withholding support.
Suggesting futility.
That's an act of treason.
[FLEGEL] And, not only would
that make you a traitor,
it would implicate
your family as well.
Flegel.
It appears even the youth are
hungry with the desire to fight.
The fine young folks
of our Empire demand
that we punish such treachery.
Fine. Although
my abilities are modest,
I accept your request.
However...
[SCHNEIDER]
He did agree to your conditions
to follow military regulations.
Is that inadequate?
[MERKATZ chuckles]
Lieutenant Commander Schneider.
You're naïve in your age.
The duke's response
to my request was merely
a cheap form of lip service.
It's only a matter of time
before he despises me
even more than he does
Marquis Lohengramm.
That can't be.
Privilege is
the worst poison of all
because it rots away
a person's spirit.
Of course, the higher nobility
has been steeping in it
for dozens of generations now.
The old game
of justifying themselves
while blaming others
for their misdeeds
has become instinctive to them.
In the past I was blind to it.
However, once I encountered
our men in the lower ranks,
I began to understand.
[NARRATOR]
In his entire life,
Merkatz had never struggled
to find the right words
as much as he did that night.
[NARRATOR] The letter
he wrote was filled with love
in every sentence.
For it was a farewell
to his wife and children.
[BRAUNSCHWEIG]
Assassination?!
Don't be ridiculous!
I have over 3,000 noblemen
who all answered
my call to assemble.
They've already begun to move.
I'm taking the
righteous initiative.
Why would you suggest
trying to assassinate--
Your Excellency, please listen!
I intend to defeat
that golden-haired brat
in a properly-fought
head-to-head confrontation
for all to see.
Once I emerge triumphantly,
my success will affirm
the strengths of my virtue
and ability beyond reproach!
And yet, you two
wish to sully my honor
with such a cowardly
recommendation?
[STREIT]
Not at all, sir!
It pains me to say it,
but the truth is our adversary
is widely known as
a genius tactician.
Sacrifices will be inevitable,
and even if we win,
sir, we'd still be endangering
the lives of all our people.
What do you mean, "even if
we win," you defeatist?!
I have no need for men who lack
faith in our assured victory!
Despicable.
Ansbach, where are you?!
Remove this useless
trash at once!
[STREIT growls]
Thank you all for coming here.
I appreciate it.
This affair will be kept
in confidence from the duke.
[FELLNER] We can't approach
Marquis Lohengramm
with these numbers,
but we should be able
to take his sister,
Countess Grünewald, hostage.
[gasps]
We've been found out!
[SOLDIERS gasping]
--[SOLDIER 16B grunts]
--[FELLNER] Retreat immediately!
--[SOLDIER 16C groans]
--Retre--
[REINHARD] You wish
to serve under my command?
Tell me.
What was it that persuaded
you to swing your loyalty
so abruptly, abandoning
your long-held allegiance
to the Duke?
It's my belief that
someone should only offer
their loyalty to
those who are able
to truly comprehend
it's worth, sir.
My, how impudent of you to say.
Fine then.
Take him, Oberstein.
I leave this man in your charge.
Right.
--[whip cracking]
--[SOLDIER 16D grunting]
[FLEGEL]
What a disgrace!
Such treachery.
A disgustingly shameful display!
See, Uncle?
Disobedient soldiers who defy us
and act on their own accord
deserve to be punished!
Right. I'll make sure
to discipline
him properly as well.
Pardon, Your Excellency.
Respectively,
we need to leave at once.
Evacuating Odin is
more pressing, sir.
Enemies could strike at any time
now that we're compromised.
We should retreat
while we still can.
Then regroup at the domain.
[BRAUNSCHWEIG]
Well, what are you waiting for?
Stop babbling, Ansbach!
Hurry!
I've received reports confirming
that Duke Braunschweig and his
family have managed to escape.
The remaining noblemen will
soon attempt to do the same.
Their most likely
destination is Geiersburg.
In regards to our
covert operations.
The mission to infiltrate
the rebel forces
has been proceeding
according to plan.
I believe the time
is ripe for battle.
[NARRATOR] All the admirals
who received the order
from Reinhard launched
into action at once.
[NARRATOR] Moving first,
Bittenfeld led a group
of armed soldiers
to occupy the Ministry of War.
[EHRENBERG] Who gave you
permission to enter here?
I haven't the faintest
idea of what you want.
But it's evident
you have no interest
in observing proper decorum.
I do apologize.
I'll make myself
perfectly clear.
We wish for everyone
to know it's a new age.
So wake up,
the times are changing.
[EHRENBERG growls]
[NARRATOR] After
detaining Military Chief
of Staff Ehrenberg,
they then seized the Supreme
Command Headquarters,
detaining its chief,
Fleet Admiral Steinhof.
Any word?
Sir, everything's clear.
[NARRATOR]
Meanwhile, at the space harbor,
soldiers under Mittermeyer's
command stood in wait
to catch any nobles who
were attempting to flee.
In satellite orbit above Odin,
all surrounding airspace was
completely secured by fleets
led by Wahlen and Kempff.
[NARRATOR]
Among the nobles they captured
was Vice Admiral Streit.
I've received
an interesting report.
Our intelligence states that you
were the man who advised
Duke Braunschweig
to assassinate me.
Is this true?
[STREIT]
It is.
[REINHARD]
So. You admit it.
And why would you
suggest such a thing?
Because I knew
this would happen.
I wanted to prevent the
chaos of a useless war.
If only my lordship were willing
to listen to sound reasoning.
This is certainly the
most regrettable of outcomes.
Regrettable for the House
of Duke Braunschweig.
And for the entire
Goldenbaum Dynasty.
Remove the man's handcuffs.
[gasps]
It would be a shame to kill him.
I'll grant you a permit
for safe passage.
You may return to your master.
Go on. Fulfill your duty.
[STREIT]
Actually, sir.
If it pleases Your Excellency,
may I have permission
to remain here on Odin?
Explain.
If I returned to my lordship,
he would immediately suspect me
of collusion and punish me.
Unfortunately, he is a man who
abandoned the vast majority
of his devoted people
in order to save himself.
Loyalty is meaningless to him.
I understand.
Would you consider serving
under my command, then?
It's a generous offer,
but I'm afraid I have no desire
to make an enemy of
my former master
Please, forgive me.
[NARRATOR] Emperor Erwin
Josef the Second bestowed
a new title upon Reinhard.
Supreme Commander
of the Imperial Navy.
Thus granting him
complete dictatorial control
regarding the Military.
By order, you are to subjugate
Duke Braunschweig and
his conspiring cohorts.
For the Empire.
Sir.
[ROYAL CLERK 16A]
Your Excellency. Please wait!
Sorry to disturb you,
but we need to determine
a proper public name
for the enemy force.
[REINHARD]
A name?
Yes, sir.
A designation for
any official records.
Apparently, they've
dubbed themselves
the "League of Just Lords."
There is only one name
befitting of their kind.
Call them the traitors.
The traitors, you say?
Very good, we'll use that, then.
[REINHARD]
Go forth and publish my decree
throughout all of the Empire.
Ensure that the enemy
forces are informed
of this as well. Tell them,
"You are now all traitors."
We'll be parting ways now.
At least for a while.
Right.
Soon, Kircheis.
Soon, the entire universe
will belong to us.
[KIRCHEIS]
Indeed. Every part of it.
All within your grasp.
But until then,
best of luck, Reinhard.
[NARRATOR] Next time on Legend
of the Galactic Heroes:
Die Neue These, episode 17:
"The Yang Fleet Mobilizes."