[ANNEROSE]
Sieg.
I hope you'll be good friends
with my brother.
[ANNEROSE]
It has been a while, Reinhard.
I hope you are doing well.
Thanks to you, I have
been enjoying my days
in peace and quiet.
The other afternoon,
I baked a lovely
Kelsey plum cake.
Just like the ones I would
make when you boys were young.
The two of you
always sang my praises
while happily eating away.
How nostalgic.
It was so long ago that it
almost seems like a dream.
Sometimes, I wonder if
it was only my imagination.
My dearest Reinhard,
don't ever forget to hold
and appreciate those
things dear to you.
Never let go of what's
important in your heart.
There may be moments
where you find it both
difficult and bothersome,
but rather than take
those things for granted,
cherish them while you can
so you are not filled
with regret if they vanish.
Speaking of which,
you have a friend
to lean and rely on.
Talk everything over with Sieg,
and listen to what he tells you.
Please be sure to take good
care of yourself out there.
I eagerly await the day
you both return home.
Until we meet again.
[beep]
[KIRCHEIS] High Admiral
Kircheis, requesting entry.
Exemplary work out there--
welcome back.
You must be spent.
Shall I call for coffee
or for wine?
It's a shame we don't have
any of my sister's cake.
[KIRCHEIS]
Reinhard. We need to talk.
Go on.
It's about Westerland.
And the two million citizens
who were massacred there.
What about them?
I've heard rumors
that you knew about this plan.
Yet you chose to play
politics and allowed them
to carry it out.
Is that the truth?
[KIRCHEIS] For what reason
did you seek supremacy?
Was it not to establish a just
regime where true impartiality
could exist, and abolish the old
ways of the Goldenbaum Dynasty?
I don't need to be hearing
such things from you.
The nobles have been
doing as they please
for nearly five centuries.
Their inevitable fall
was bound to be messy.
Resistance and
bloodshed was expected.
However...
Civilians were not
part of the nobility's debt.
There was no reason
for their blood to be spilt.
Without a liberated public
as it's foundation,
the new order cannot stand.
If you sacrifice
the people for political gain,
is it not the same as
digging out the ground
from under your own feet?
I told you, I realize that!
[KIRCHEIS] When you
sacrifice innocent lives,
you stain your hands with blood.
And there's no amount
of flowery rhetoric
that can ever wash it off.
Why would you deign
to stoop so low?
To dishonor yourself.
For the sake of some
momentary advantage?
I have had enough
of your lecturing!
First of all, Kircheis,
at what point did I request your
opinion regarding this matter?
[REINHARD] I'm asking you,
when did I invite your input?
Apologies. I gave it unprompted.
[REINHARD]
That's right.
You may share your opinions
only when I ask for them.
What's done is done.
Leave it be.
With all due respect, Reinhard.
What the nobles did was
certainly unforgivable.
That much is true.
But you chose
to turn a blind eye.
Tell me, which of those
two is the greater sin?
Kircheis!
Yes, sir?
Remind me, Admiral.
What are you to me?
I am nothing but
your faithful subordinate,
Your Excellency.
[NOBLE 22A sighs]
Another suicide?
[NOBLE 22B] Many others
have been imprisoned.
If only they'd surrendered.
[NOBLE 22A]
But even if they had,
would Marquis Lohengramm
have accepted them?
[NOBLE 22C]
How could this have happened?
What was the
coalition leader thinking?
[BRAUNSCHWEIG]
Nothing to worry about.
If they did better
in that last skirmish,
it was only because they
happened to have luck on
their side.
Of course, the real battle
has yet to begin.
Truer words have
never been spoken, Uncle!
[LANDSBERG]
And next time,
we'll give them the greatest
fight of the century!
Very good.
We'll destroy that golden-haired
brat once and for all.
And then we'll make a goblet
out of his pathetic skull!
[ALL]
Prosit!
[HILDA]
Since the fall of Westerland,
distrust in Duke Braunschweig
has been growing exponentially.
Both among the nobility
and the bureaucracy.
Additionally,
I fear Duke Lichtenlade
is scheming something,
as he has been visiting
with nobles throughout
the imperial capital.
Please be careful.
I'll pray for your success.
[OBERSTEIN]
I would advise against giving
Admiral Kircheis
special treatment.
[OBERSTEIN] His military
accomplishments are too great.
It's true that his work
in subjugating
the outlying starzones
was a considerable factor
in our victory,
allowing you soley to focus on
fighting the Noble's Coalition--
However.
To make him the vanguard in
the final battle on top of that.
[REINHARD]
It's not "special treatment."
If the universe
turned against me,
Kircheis would remain
standing by my side.
His support has
always been a constant.
I've simply been rewarding
him for his loyalty.
What's so wrong about that?
Excellency.
I trust you understand that
I am by no means suggesting that
you purge, exile, or harm High
Admiral Kircheis in any way.
But an organization does
not need a number two.
Regardless of their competence.
They are a detriment to the
balance of the entire group.
A figure that could distract
from the men's loyalty
to the number one
should not exist.
I've heard enough.
Stop badgering me.
[OBERSTEIN] The Noble's
Coalition has been successfully
cornered and our intel
has reason to believe
an all-out attack
against us is imminent.
In other words,
this will most likely be
the final battle.
Regarding our strategy,
I will now assign each of you
your role in this operation
against the traitors.
High Admiral Siegfried Kircheis.
[KIRCHEIS]
Sir.
[OBERSTEIN]
You are to serve as vanguard.
Your role in the impeding
battle will be crucial.
There was something off
between the two of them today.
Kircheis and the Marquis.
During any other meeting, the
fleet admiral would've given
Kircheis the orders himself.
But Oberstein stepped in
and got involved this time.
The Chief of Staff doesn't seem
too fond of the fact that
His Excellency defers to
Kircheis in both his public
and personal life.
Of course,
it's not as though I don't
understand his frustration.
Oberstein is certainly
a clever man,
I'll give him that. But he
seems to have a bad habit
of stirring up trouble
when there wasn't any.
Besides, there's no need
to try and fix something
if it wasn't broken
in the first place.
Especially when it comes
to human relationships.
In any case.
The important thing
is we win this battle.
Everything else can wait.
You've ordered our deployment?!
Do you take issue with that?
We should instead be using
the fortress to our advantage.
Let the enemy exhaust
themselves and wait for
the tide of battle to change.
What purpose would
it serve for us to spread out?
[FLEGEL] You forget that you're
a high noble in name alone!
Know your place, peasant!
Nonsense!
You forget the duke
and I are comrades,
--not master and servant.
--[growls]
[FAHRENHEIT]
Regardless of title,
we are fellow guardians
of the Galactic Empire,
whose goal is to protect the
Goldenbaum Dynasty from
the tyranny of
Marquis Lohengramm.
We ought to be united
by this shared purpose.
I merely offer my insight
as a military specialist
in the hope of avoiding
the worst possible outcome.
Yet, you force your will
upon us, as if giving orders!
I'm afraid you've
misunderstood your role,
Duke Braunschweig!
[BRAUNSCHWEIG growls]
I've no use for any cowards!
All ships deploy!
No more faffing about!
You will bring me back
the head of that
golden-haired brat at once!
The enemy appears
to be on the move.
Tell Kircheis it's time
to get into position.
All ships.
Full speed ahead!
[NARRATOR] The Noble's Coalition
deployed their forces
with Flegel leading the charge.
All rushing forward
in perfect formation.
Tonight, they shall
all taste the outrage
we have been forced to endure!
[FLEGEL]
Fire!
[FLEGEL gasps]
The Barbarossa?
[OBERSTEIN] Their advance guard
seems to have collapsed.
All right. Next wave, launch.
That's Mittermeyer, followed
by Reuenthal, then Bittenfeld,
and we'll finish with Kempff.
Rear line.
Wahlen and Mecklinger
will focus to their front,
whereas Lutz will defend
us from the back.
Remember to attack in waves.
It's imperative we crush
the enemy's will to fight.
[CREWMEN screaming]
[FLEGEL growls]
[COMMS. OFFICER 22A]
Incoming transmission!
Perhaps they'll surrender?
Open the comm lines.
[FLEGEL]
Admiral Reuenthal, I presume?
This is Baron Flegel speaking.
I'm requesting one-on-one combat
between my battleship and yours.
[gasps]
[FLEGEL] Our worthy spirit
and loyalty to the Empire
holds steadfast and true!
I will prove this to you myself.
This is pointless.
End feed.
Hold on, I wasn't--
[FLEGEL]
That bastard!
A filthy low-born like him could
never understand the pride
of the nobility!
I can't believe this.
Is there not a single soldier
among the enemy ranks with
the backbone to
face me one-on-one?
Find someone immediately!
[SCHUMACHER]
That's enough.
[FLEGEL]
Ah!
Nobody is going to fight
with you, Your Excellency.
As the Admiral said,
there would be nothing to gain
from accepting your challenge.
Instead, we should find
a safe place to fall back.
Let's cut our losses
and be grateful
that we still have our lives.
[FLEGEL] Silence!
I am not afraid of death.
I wish only for a beautiful end
befitting of an imperial noble!
[SCHUMACHER] It's because of
this nonsense you preach
that we've lost this war.
[FLEGEL]
Excuse me?!
[SCHUMACHER] If you wish to
chase delusions of grandeur,
go right ahead.
But spare us all.
We've no reason to die.
Least of all for your pride.
Traitor!
[gunshot]
[FLEGEL grunting]
Long live the Em--
[coughs]
The Empire...
[SCHNEIDER]
Please stop, Your Excellency.
[MERKATZ]
Lieutenant Commander.
You had me concerned,
so I removed the energy
capsule from your weapon,
as a precaution.
This is precisely how
I feared things would end up.
I did all I could
to avoid this fate,
but in the end, I simply
postponed the inevitable.
Either way, when did
you unload my firearm?
Somehow, I didn't
notice you taking it.
Well, you really had me fooled.
Are you that determined
to keep me alive, Schneider?
[SCHNEIDER]
Yes, Admiral, I am.
Tell me.
What am I to do
with my life now?
Marquis Lohengramm
has yet to take full control
of the universe, sir.
There's still places in it
that are outside his reach.
You must seek asylum
and regain your strength
to strike back!
Are you suggesting
that I defect?
[SCHNEIDER]
It's our only hope.
Since you've
proposed a comeback,
the Dominion of Fezzan must not
be your destination of choice.
[MERKATZ] So then...
The Free Planets Alliance?
Yes.
But I've been battling
against their people
for well over 40 years.
Countless numbers of my men
have died by their hands
just as they've died by ours.
I wonder if they could accept a
man like me among their ranks.
We should place our
confidence in Yang Wen-li.
He may be unconventional,
but I've heard he has
a benevolent mind.
If he should refuse,
you won't be alone.
I will follow you until death.
You fool.
Your whole life's ahead of you.
With a talent like yours,
Marquis Lohengramm is sure
to grant you an
esteemed position.
Those are kind words,
and I've nothing against him,
but I've already decided that
you alone are my superior.
Please, sir.
Give me your decision.
Then I'll entrust
myself to you, Lieutenant.
Let's contact Yang Wen-li.
[gasps]
[REINHARD] It's just as
Fraulein Mariendorf said.
She predicted this civil war,
as well as the commoners
revolting and bringing victory.
She couldn't have
been more accurate.
The speed at which this resolved
exceeded my expectations.
Fortunately, that only bodes
poorly for the traitors, not us.
It appears that
the enemies in front
have lost their strength.
We should return to Odin
and prepare to engage those
opposing us at the rear.
[OBERSTEIN]
Sir.
--[booming]
--[alarm sounding]
[BRAUNSCHWEIG whimpers]
[ANSBACH]
My lord.
Is that you, Ansbach?
I thought you were
still imprisoned!
Forgive me, sir,
but my soldiers rescued me.
What has become of my family?!
They're all right.
I have ensured their safe
passage to a secure location.
Ah, very good.
--I'll join them--
--[ANSBACH] Come with us, sir.
[alarm blaring]
[sighs]
Well, here we are.
What exactly have you arranged?
My sincere condolences, sir.
But given our current
set of circumstances,
I'm afraid you're left with
a difficult decision to make,
Your Excellency.
[BRAUNSCHWEIG] Hm. I suppose our
only choice is to broker peace.
[ANSBACH]
You wish to negotiate?
Offering favorable
conditions, of course.
I will give him
my daughter Elizabeth
as an official gesture
of recognition.
This would make him the late
kaiser's grandson by marriage,
thereby giving him
the proper status to succeed
as a rightful heir.
[ANSBACH]
A futile suggestion.
[gasps]
That might have
worked months ago,
but as of this moment,
Marquis Lohengramm clearly
has no need of your assistance.
[BRAUNSCHWEIG gasps]
[ANSBACH] He will rise to
power through his own merits.
It's unlikely anyone
can stop him.
[BRAUNSCHWEIG]
I am Duke Otto von Braunschweig.
I'm the head of the most
prestigious elite family
in the whole of the Empire!
Despite all that,
are you suggesting
that golden- haired brat
means to kill me?
That is the exact
reason he cannot
allow you to live.
You're an enemy to humanity.
[BRAUNSCHWEIG]
Humanity? How so?
I refer to Westerland of course.
I would hope you
hadn't forgotten already.
[BRAUNSCHWEIG] Culling away
a few low-born peasants
is hardly a crime!
As both an aristocrat
and their ruler,
I was merely exercising
my god-given rights!
[ANSBACH] Yes, the Galactic
Empire may have operated
under that mode of
logic for centuries.
However, from now on,
that thinking is
going to die out.
For him to demonstrate that,
the Marquis has no choice.
He'll make sure
you die along with it.
[BRAUNSCHWEIG whimpers]
Therefore,
as the last living leader
of the Braunschweig family,
I implore you to end
your reign with dignity.
[rumbling]
[BRAUNSCHWEIG sighs]
Very well, then.
I shall pass with grace.
However, I can't
bear to permit that
golden-haired scoundrel
to usurp the throne!
If I'm going to Hell,
then I'm bringing that
bastard with me!
Listen, Ansbach,
You must do whatever you can
to stop him from
claiming the crown!
If you can assure me that much,
I'll take my own life without
any lingering regrets!
Please, promise
you'll kill him for me!
As you command.
I swear it.
I'll eradicate Marquis
Lohengramm at all costs.
Thank you.
All right.
Be gentle.
I don't want to feel any pain.
[ANSBACH]
Sir.
You'll start to grow drowsy.
And drift off into a deep sleep.
[BRAUNSCHWEIG whimpers]
[wails]
No!
No! I refuse!
I don't want to die after all!
I'll surrender to him!
He can have
my title or my fortune,
but not my life!
Ah-- Ahh!
What are you doing?!
You ruffians!
Get your hands
off me this instant!
[gasps]
[BRAUNSCHWEIG whimpers]
You must.
[BRAUNSCHWEIG gasps]
[BRAUNSCHWEIG panting]
[BRAUNSCHWEIG grunts]
[choking, rasping]
[ANSBACH] Take him to
the infirmary at once.
[OFFICER 22A] But sir,
he's already passed, hasn't he?
[ANSBACH]
You'll do as you're told.
[OFFICER 22A]
Understood, Commodore.
[ANSBACH] With this,
the Goldenbaum Dynasty
has truly fallen.
What follows will become
known as the Age of Grünewald.
Or will it?
[NARRATOR] Next time on
Legend of the Galactic Heroes:
Die Neue These: Episode 23,
"Farewell to the Days of Old."