Pardon the delay, sir.
What is it?
[GUARD 23A] Armaments are
prohibited beyond this point.
I must ask you
to leave your weapon.
I am High Admiral
Siegfried Kircheis.
Am I still forbidden
from bearing arms?
Unfortunately,
no exceptions can be made,
not even one for yourself, sir.
Those were our orders.
I do apologize.
No need. It's fine.
I'll comply.
This was never an issue before.
Hasn't he always maintained
special permission to carry?
[VOLKER] It seems the
circumstances have changed.
[KIRCHEIS]
I must be patient with him.
He may falter and make
the occasional mistake.
But surely he'll come
back to his senses.
I've been at his side
for over a decade,
and he's always come back.
I genuinely thought
it would be like this forever,
but... could I have been wrong?
[HERALD 23A]
Now presenting his excellency,
Marquis Reinhard von Lohengramm,
Supreme Commander
of the Galactic Empire!
[NARRATOR]
In the year IC 488,
a victory ceremony was
held at Geiersburg Fortress,
with prisoners of war
being granted an audience
with the marquis.
Adalbert von Fahrenheit.
What a surprise.
I haven't seen you since
the Battle of Astarte.
[FAHRENHEIT]
Sir.
You chose to ally with the likes
of Duke Braunschweig?
What an
uncharacteristic mistake.
I have a proposal.
Why not swear your allegiance
and serve with my forces?
I remain a soldier
of the Empire.
Now that you've asserted your
authority over its military,
I shall humbly accept.
I may have taken a longer path
to reach this position,
but I intend to
compensate for wasted time.
Then you should join
my ranks as admiral.
Heh. Imagine giving your
master's cold corpse
as a present.
[gasping]
[ANSBACH]
Marquis Lohengramm!
[growls, gasps]
This is your demise!
I will avenge my lord even
if it's the last thing I do!
[ANSBACH, KIRCHEIS groaning]
Augh!
[KIRCHEIS grunts]
[gasps]
[WAHLEN growls]
[WAHLEN]
Don't let him get away!
[BITTENFELD]
You aren't going anywhere!
Medic! Call a medic, now!
[KIRCHEIS]
It's... too late...
[gasps]
[ANSBACH laughs]
Sorry, Duke Braunschweig.
You'll have to forgive me.
I made you a promise,
and yet, I failed to fulfill it.
It's a shame you'll
still have to wait
a few more years to see that
golden-haired brat in Hell!
[grunts]
You blathering fool!
That's enough nonsense!
[ANSBACH]
But at the very least...
...you'll still have
me to keep you company.
No!
[ANSBACH retches, gags]
[REINHARD]
Kircheis...?
Is that... you, Reinhard...?
Are you... all right...?
[KIRCHEIS]
I...
I don't... think I can be...
of much use to you... anymore.
Please forgive me....
Stop that! What are you saying?!
The doctor's almost here.
You'll be healed up
before you know it.
That's right.
Then we can visit my sister
and tell her how we won.
Well? How about it?
Lord Reinhard...
[REINHARD]
You need to save your energy!
Make it yours,
claim the universe.
Yeah.
[KIRCHEIS]
Also...
Please tell Annerose...
Tell her that I...
That Sieg...
He did what she asked.
He kept his promise.
[REINHARD] No! I will tell
her nothing of the sort!
Whatever it is,
you can say it yourself!
Are you listening to me?!
I won't be your messenger--
that's simply unnecessary!
We'll see my sister together!
The two of us! Right?
Kircheis?
[KIRCHEIS sighs]
Why won't you...
Why won't you answer?
Kircheis...
Kircheis...?
Say something!
Answer me!
Please, sir. He's gone now.
Come then.
Allow him to rest in peace.
[REINHARD] Don't you dare
lie to me, Mittermeyer.
He couldn't possibly be gone!
[gasps]
Because he wouldn't.
He'd never even dream
of leaving me behind!
No... He's wrong, Kircheis...
Wake up.
I said open your eyes.
[REINHARD]
Kircheis!
[REUENTHAL] It's already been
three days since the incident.
We can't maintain
this gag order.
Remaining silent in
communications with Odin
does not bode well for us.
If I may speak frankly here,
I was honestly surprised
to see that the Marquis
was so emotionally fragile.
[MITTERMEYER] He wouldn't've
carried on like this
if it had been you or I.
[MITTERMEYER]
Siegfried Kircheis is special.
Or, was special.
The Marquis truly
lost half of his own self.
And all due to his
own folly, no less.
We must hope that
Marquis Lohengramm will recover.
No. We need him to
Given his current state,
we'll soon end up lost in space,
singing our imminent destruction
into the galactic abyss.
All right. So what are
we supposed to do?
How do we get him
back on his feet?
[MECKLINGER] If there's
anyone with a solution,
it's that man.
[BITTENFELD]
Which man?
You know who.
The only one who's not here.
Do we genuinely need to
seek him out for counsel?
We have no choice.
He's nothing
without the Marquis.
I'm certain that even he
is well aware of that fact.
He'll be obliged to help us.
Which means, ultimately,
we'll owe our wiseman a favor.
That's troublesome.
What happens if this puts
him in a position to start
taking advantage of us?
[REUENTHAL]
If Marquis Lohengramm is a ship,
then every one of us,
including Oberstein, is on it.
If we want to save ourselves,
then we have to save our leader.
Should matters come to it,
and our intelligent chief
of staff tries to profit from
our time of need,
then we'll retaliate using
whatever measures necessary.
[grunting]
[OFFICER 23A] Vice Admiral
Oberstein has arrived.
It's been quite some time,
and yet, it appears you're no
closer to reaching a consensus.
With our navy's number one
and number two absent,
we currently lack leadership.
As you might imagine,
we're at a loss.
So I don't suppose you have
something to contribute?
I just might.
Well?
We ought to request assistance
from the Marquis' sister.
You suggest we ask
Countess Grünewald?
The subject was
brought up earlier, but--
[OBERSTEIN] Allow me to
assume that responsibility.
And I have an undertaking
to assign you as well.
I'd like you to capture
the man who killed
High Admiral Kircheis.
Immediately.
What a strange thing to say.
Didn't we all watch Ansbach die?
[OBERSTEIN]
He played a minor part.
We'll make an official
statement that the mastermind
was someone else.
Someone much more significant.
Who, then?
The Prime Minister,
Duke Lichtenlade.
[gasping]
I'd surely never want to make
an enemy out of you.
Victory would be impossible.
Our allegiance with the man
was always temporary
and his elimination inevitable.
Also, it's not as though he has
been conducting operations
with the purest of intentions.
There's no question.
He's been concocting his own
devious plan to sabotage
Marquis Lohengramm.
In other words,
the charges wouldn't
be completely false.
[OBERSTEIN] You must return
to Odin as soon as possible.
You'll arrest Duke Lichtenlade.
And take the state seal.
After that, we can establish
his excellency as dictator.
But whoever
obtains the seal first
could just choose to stay
in the capital, right?
What would happen if they tried
to claim leadership themselves?
[OBERSTEIN]
Hardly a concern.
If anyone acted
on such an ambition,
they would be swiftly
compromised by
the other admirals.
None of you would
resign yourselves to submit.
Especially not to
an officer of equal rank.
It's exactly why
I've always thought
having a second-in-command
was unnecessary.
[REUENTHAL]
Well.
Power is not justified
by how you acquire it.
The only thing that matters
is the way in which
you choose to wield it.
Meaning that a bit
of scheming is unavoidable.
[REUENTHAL]
It's decided.
We shall seize the chance to
purge Marquis Lohengramm's
enemies and reclaim absolute
supremacy in his name.
[MITTERMEYER]
Leave the stragglers behind.
They'll all find their way
to Odin eventually.
[NARRATOR] The fleet was
20,000 ships strong when it left
from Geiersburg Fortress.
It shrank more and more
passing through each warp.
By the time it reached
the capital planet Odin,
the fleet's numbers
dwindled down to 3,000.
[BITTENFELD]
Disregard ground control.
Land in any space you can find,
even if it's in a lake!
[crashing]
[LICHTENLADE gasps]
What's going on?
Why are you heathens
making such a ruckus?
[REUENTHAL]
Duke Lichtenlade.
We're officially placing
you under arrest.
On what grounds?
You are wanted for the charge
of attempted assassination
against Marquis Reinhard
von Lohengramm.
[LICHTENLADE]
You buffoon!
What evidence could you even
possess to prove such nonsense?
I'm the Imperial Prime Minister!
In case you've forgotten,
I stand above all of you
as counsel to the Kaiser!
That may be so,
but the fact remains
that you're nothing but
a filthy conspirator.
Lock him up!
[MITTERMEYER]
Where is the state seal?
Under what authority
would you even dare
to ask me such a bold question?
This is the protective chamber
where it's held, but you--
[VAULT GUARD 23A]
Stop this at once!
This is unconscionable!
Have you no respect for
the Empire's Imperial Family
and its power?
Your behavior is completely
unbecoming and you all
should be ashamed of y--
[MITTERMEYER]
The imperial family's power?
I suppose that
existed once upon a time.
But true power is
determined by capability.
It shouldn't ever happen
the other way around.
[SOLDIER 23A]
We found it!
Here it is.
So this is the seal.
[MAID 23A] Where did
that army come from, milady?
[HILDA] Well, it didn't
appear out of thin air.
I'm sure they serve
Marquis Lohengramm.
No one else could
lead so many people.
[HILDA] The winds of change
are ushering in a new age.
The world may experience
some turbulence,
but that's far better
than remaining stagnant.
[giggling]
[ANNEROSE]
So what do you think of it?
Does it taste good?
--[KIRCHEIS] Mm-hmm!
--Perfect!
[gasps]
[REINHARD]
Kircheis!
[gasps]
[door whirs]
Pardon the intrusion,
Your Excellency.
I'm here to inform you of
a message we've received
from the capital.
[REINHARD]
From whom?
[OBERSTEIN]
Right, sir.
It's from your sister,
Countess Grünewald.
[REINHARD]
Damn it!
How dare you?!
You went around my back and told
her without my permission!
[OBERSTEIN]
Yes, I did.
You've absolutely
crossed the line!
Perhaps.
But try as one might,
the simple truth is that
you cannot hide forever.
[REINHARD]
Enough!
Could it be that you're
afraid of your sister?
[REINHARD]
Tch. Why would--
If that is not the case,
I urge you to speak
with her at once.
As you can clearly see,
I have not abandoned you.
Your self-flagellation
is commendable.
I'm quite grateful you
haven't forced the burden
of responsibility onto me.
However, if you
continue to wallow
in the past and fail to stand
tall and face the future,
then this will be
where your story ends--
with the universe
in someone else's hands.
As for Admiral Kircheis,
he will look down upon you
from Valhalla in disgrace.
[growling]
Annerose...
Hello, my poor,
darling Reinhard.
How tragic.
I suppose there's no longer
anybody left for you to lose.
Not a single soul.
No. I'll always
have you, after all.
Isn't that still true?
I have you!
[ANNEROSE] Yes. And of course,
I have you as well.
Both of us have nothing
left but each other.
[gasps]
[ANNEROSE]
Reinhard.
I'm going to leave
the Schwarzen mansion.
I'd like to find
a small cottage somewhere.
Why would...
[ANNEROSE] Also, we should
keep to ourselves for a while.
But Sister--!
I think...
...it's best if I
seclude myself from you.
The two of us live
very different lives.
Now in my life,
there's only the past.
But in yours...
You have the whole future.
If you're tired,
come and visit me anytime.
Of course, you mustn't
grow too weary just yet,
dear brother.
I understand.
If that's truly what you desire,
then I will do as you please.
Once I've claimed the universe,
I'll come by and see you.
However, there's
something I wanted to ask.
[REINHARD]
Before we part, please tell me.
Did you... love Kircheis?
[REINHARD]
I've been briefed on our status.
On the day that
all of you set out,
Oberstein gave me a full report.
Sir.
You'll be duly rewarded
for your distinguished service.
I'm currently en route
to Odin myself.
We've apprehended
Duke Lichtenlade's family.
They're all in confinement,
and they are now anticipating
your judgment.
[REINHARD]
You needn't wait for my arrival.
I'm entrusting
all of you to punish them.
Understood?
[REUENTHAL]
Very well.
And what would you have us
do with the Duke himself?
We can't very well execute
the Imperial Prime Minister.
Encourage his suicide.
Via the most painless
method possible.
[REUENTHAL]
Noted.
Now then, how should we
proceed with the relatives?
[REINHARD] Banish women
and children to the frontier.
Put all men over
the age of ten to death.
Yes, sir.
Ages nine and under
are not to be harmed, then?
I myself was ten years old
when I first started school.
Anybody younger than that
has yet to fully mature.
So they are exempt.
Of course, they're welcome
to try and strike me down
once they've grown up.
It's only natural that
an incompetent leader
should be overthrown.
[laughs]
The same goes for you.
If you have the
confidence to defeat me,
then by all means, attempt it.
You can have at me
any time you like.
Surely you're joking.
I'll be taking my leave, then.
[REINHARD]
Superb work.
[OBERSTEIN]
Your Excellency.
Are you certain that is
what you want to do
with the Lichtenlade family?
I've shed a considerable
amount of blood
in my lifetime.
And I will surely shed more.
I don't see how
adding a few more drops
from their family
makes any difference.
It's negligible in the end.
If it pleases you,
then so be it.
[NARRATOR] Having lost Kircheis,
and now his sister,
Reinhard's entire being
was starved with yearning.
Even if he became the
absolute ruler of all humanity,
would that satisfy
the hunger in his heart?
The answer appeared doubtful.
It seemed his incredible
longing could not be satisfied.
Perhaps... it never would.
And thus, Reinhard was left
with no other path to follow.
He could only counter his
melancholy with warfare.
By continuing to fight, win,
and conquer in an endless cycle.
But for that,
he would need an enemy.
The stronger and more
competent they were,
the more he could forget the
pain of his ravenous heartache.
And he had the strongest,
most competent enemy
he could ever hope for
in the Free Planets Alliance.
[NARRATOR] Next time on
Legend of the Galactic Heroes:
Die Neue These, Episode 24:
"My Friend."