[GREENHILL]
The 12 jewels that protect
the capital planet Heinessen.
[GREENHILL] We still
have Artemis's Necklace,
and that's an incredible
last line of defense.
So long as those satellites
still orbit Heinessen,
not even Yang Wen-li
can penetrate
its gravitational field.
We must keep faith.
We haven't lost this yet.
[door beeping]
[YANG]
Come in.
Commander Baghdash reporting.
As requested.
I've finally thought of
a job that I can have you do.
[BAGHDASH]
Sir! I am at your service.
If you ordered it, I would even
infiltrate Heinessen itself.
Really now?
And would you then run right
back to Admiral Greenhill?
Sir. Please, I wouldn't
dream of such a thing.
[YANG]
That was a joke.
I'd like for you
to act as a witness.
A witness? Witness to what?
The National Salvation
Military Council's coup d'état
was actually orchestrated
by Marquis Reinhard
von Lohengramm,
of the Galactic Empire.
You'll bear witness to that.
That's quite
a preposterous notion
you've come up with.
[YANG]
It's true.
I don't have any physical
evidence as of yet,
but it is a fact.
[alarm blaring]
Greetings.
I am Commander Baghdash of
the Free Planets Alliance.
Department of Intelligence.
I'm broadcasting this
message in order to share
something that will be
crucial to the future of
the Free Planets Alliance
as we know it.
I don't understand.
What is this?
Wasn't all network
access blocked?
The Yang fleet is transmitting
this video stream directly.
They're using the
frequency that's reserved
for emergency
alert broadcasts.
They are?
Truth be told,
I was sent to
assassinate Yang Wen-li.
The Military Council ordered
me to, and I humbly accepted.
But... I have since seen
the error of my ways,
and have sworn my loyalty to
the Free Planets
Alliance once again.
The reason being?
I have learned this coup d'état
was planned and executed per
the wishes of Marquis Lohengramm
of the Galactic Empire.
[BAGHDASH] The Galactic Empire
is currently embroiled in
a massive civil war, itself.
This is no mere coincidence.
Marquis Lohengramm initiated the
coup to prevent the Alliance
from exploiting the
Empire's weakened state.
Frankly, the traitor
Military Council
is nothing more than
a puppet of the Empire.
That backstabber!
He's the only
traitor around here!
He's saying we're just
the Empire's pawns in all this?
How can he proclaim such
obvious political propaganda?
I'd have thought
Yang Wen-li would be above
blatantly lying to the people.
The fact is,
we started this movement
of our own volition.
And it has been realized thanks
to the brilliant strategy
that was provided
by one of our own.
Rear Admiral Lynch.
Yet they utter such fiction,
calling us puppets.
[LYNCH chuckles]
[GREENHILL grunts]
[laughing]
Is something funny,
Rear Admiral Lynch?
I gotta admit,
I'm honored by your praise.
But sorry, I'm not the one
who came up with our plan.
What are you saying?
Then who did come up
with this elaborate plot?
[LYNCH] That spokesman of Yang
Wen-li was right on the nose.
This coup d'état you worked so
hard for was all the brain child
of that blonde brat.
The Imperial
Commander and Chief,
otherwise known as Marquis
Reinhard von Lohengramm.
[LYNCH] He wanted to stir up
some infighting within
the Alliance while he takes
care of the opposing nobility
through their own civil war.
Do you mean to tell me
we've been playing the part
of Marquis Lohengramm's jesters?
Dancing in the palm of
his hand this whole time?
Heh. Yep, and you guys
put on quite the recital.
Everything was going
according to his plan,
but now I've found
myself stuck between
a rock and a hard place.
Because, apparently,
you were all too incompetent
and they found us out.
Why would you do this?
What's the reason?
Did he offer you some
irresistible reward
for your success?
Yeah, he did, actually.
But that wasn't the only draw.
I won't name any names,
so let's just say...
...I wanted to
make a lot of hopelessly
self-righteous people
experience humiliation that
no amount of excuses could fix.
So how does it feel,
Admiral Greenhill?
Knowing this precious
National Salvation
Military Council of yours
was nothing but a tool for
the most ambitious man
in the Galactic Empire?
[beep]
[COMMS. OFFICER 12A]
Chairman!
Multiple flying
objects approaching
at high speed have
been detected!
Our Trajectory analysis
shows that their target is
not this planet, but
Artemis's Necklace!
There are 12 in number!
[gasps]
[NARRATOR] Three hundred years
ago in the Galactic Empire,
on the bitterly
cold planet Altair VII,
there was a young republican
who was being forced to work
like a slave in the mines.
His name was Arle Heinessen.
His deepest desire was to
escape Altair VII and start
a new nation with
a republican government.
His only obstacle was
acquiring the materials
to build a spacecraft
that would carry people there.
Apparently, one day,
he saw some children playing
with boats they made out
of ice, and it came to him.
He built ships out of
the unlimited supply of dry ice
on Altair VII,
and embarked on an
exodus which became known as
the "Long March of Ten-
Thousand Light Years."
We are going to be
mimicking this legend
about Arle Heinessen,
father of our nation.
We've carved a dozen ice
floes out of Planet Srinagar.
Each has a volume
of one cubic kilometer
and weighs one billion tons.
We then equipped
each of those floes
with strong engines,
allowing them to fly
at near light speed.
An object's effective
mass increases with its speed,
and significantly at
the speed of light.
So if a billion-ton ice floe
were to crash into something
at that speed, no military
satellite would stand a chance.
Also... The ice floes and
satellites are both unmanned.
If this works, we can
take out Artemis's Necklace
without bloodshed.
I know you've
prepared 12 of them,
but should we really
destroy every satellite?
Shouldn't we at least keep
a few operational for later use?
There's no need.
The very presence of those
things is what gave
the insurgents the illusion
that they could pull off
a coup d'état.
So we'll destroy
every last one of 'em.
[GATTY] Artemis's Necklace...
is destroyed...
[GREENHILL]
This is the end of the road.
We've lost this fight.
Our military
revolution has failed.
We need to accept that.
No, it isn't over yet!
We still have Heinessen's
billion citizens,
as well as its key military
and political personnel!
There's a chance
we can still negotiate--
Give it up.
Resisting any further would not
only prove to be futile,
it would hinder
the reunification
of the nation and its people.
[GATTY] In that case... What are
we all supposed to do now?
Surrender and face
the inevitable punishment?
[GREENHILL] Those who want to
are welcome to do so.
I choose another path.
But there is one final thing
I must see to before then.
We cannot leave
behind any evidence,
any witnesses to the fact
that our noble uprising
was secretly a scheme
by the Empire.
Rear Admiral Lynch,
believe it or not,
I've always had
high hopes for you.
I have ever since cadet school,
when you were just
two classes behind me.
What transpired
at El Facil nine years ago
was truly regrettable.
I thought of you.
I had hoped that what we were
doing here could help to restore
your honor, even if
only by a small margin.
[chuckles] Well, you never did
have very good judgement.
[gunshot]
[gunshots]
[groans]
[coughs]
You're all a bunch of fools.
[sighs]
You realize I only
did that to save him
from losing his honor, right?
Couldn't even figure
out that much?
He got to go out with a bang.
It's better than living
and being put on trial.
"A man's honor."
What a joke.
[gunshot]
[EVENS]
I, Alliance Navy Captain Evens,
am speaking on behalf of
the Military Council chairman.
There's no point
in attacking us.
We have accepted our defeat
and will no longer respond
with pointless resistance.
Everything is over.
I'm glad to hear
of your decision.
However, I can't help but wonder
why you're speaking on
behalf of Admiral Greenhill.
Where is he?
I don't see him there.
He made the decision
to take his own life.
It was a perfect ending.
[YANG gasps]
[EVENS]
Admiral Yang.
You know our objective was to
purify our democratic republic,
and once we had, to wipe the
Galactic Empire's autocracy
out of existence.
It is unfortunate that
we failed to realize this ideal.
Do you understand, Admiral Yang?
You have just contributed to
the survival of autocracy!
And what exactly is autocracy?
Is it not unelected politicians?
Zero representation?
Taking away freedoms?
Controlling the public
through violence?
Because right now,
that's precisely what
you're doing on Heinessen.
You are the autocracy.
Or am I wrong?
[EVENS]
You are!
Our current power
is a temporary measure.
The government was corrupt--what
other way was there to fix that?
Corruption in government
doesn't simply come down
to politicians taking bribes.
That is corruption
of the individual.
Government corruption is a state
of affairs where politicians
are above criticism
for such an act.
Your insurgency ordered
the regulation of free speech.
Don't you think that
by that action alone,
you've lost the right to condemn
the Empire's autocracy,
as well as the corruption
of the Alliance's
current government?
We were putting
our lives and reputations
on the line.
I won't allow you to drag our
names through the mud for that.
Our cause was not one
lacking in righteousness.
The only things we did lack
were luck and capability.
Just that. Nothing more.
Is that what you believe?
To the Military Council,
we hail!
It's unfortunate
he couldn't admit
to his own mistakes,
even in the bitter end.
Proceed with
our landing preparations.
Sir.
Admiral Yang.
May I have an hour--
No, two hours to myself?
I know that I'll
be able to recover from this,
and get back on my own
two feet, but I don't
believe that I can
do so immediately.
So please, sir...
[YANG]
Of course.
[FREDERICA grunts, whimpers]
[sobs softly]
[sobs]
[sobbing continues]
I feel like an
utter embarrassment.
I was no use to you at all,
even with the information
that you had so
graciously given me.
Oh, please, sir.
You wouldn't have been
locked up for all this time
if I hadn't taken so long.
So... Is there anything
I can get for you?
Well, come to think of it,
I sure wouldn't be against
having my first bottle
of whiskey in four months.
I'll have one brought
to you immediately.
Thank you for that.
So... Do you know what
happened to Admiral Greenhill?
Yes, he passed away.
Is that so?
Seems this old man has
outlived the youth yet again.
[OFFICER 21A] Make sure
you bring these files
straight to him.
[OFFICER 21C]
We've got a meeting in five.
Then a short break and we
resume our regular duties...
[OFFICER 21B]
On my way.
There is much
we need to do, Admiral.
Informing the nation
of the coup d'état's failure
and the reinstatement
of constitutional rule,
assessing any and all damage,
apprehending the remaining
members of the Council,
--and more.
--Ugh.
My head hurts just hearing that.
You don't have time
for headaches, sir.
[beeping]
[FREDERICA]
It's Commodore Schönkopf.
[YANG]
What is it?
[WALTER] Julian's just run
into someone unexpected.
[YANG]
Who do you mean?
[WALTER] You probably don't
even want to hear his name,
but it's the High
Council Chairman.
[FREDERICA gasps]
That would be Trunicht.
[WALTER]
He found him on his way back
from escorting
Admiral Bewcock home.
Officer Machungo? Over there?
[WALTER]
He said when he found him,
Chairman Trunicht was
surrounded by members
of the Church of Terra.
[YANG]
Good grief.
Out of the frying pan
and into the fire.
He was with terraists?
[CONTROLLER 21A]
Berezka, alter your route
to the western course.
Cargo is being unloaded
on the C deck.
[KONEV]
Roger.
[RUBINSKY]
You seem to be in a bad mood.
[KONEV]
No, I always look like this.
It certainly isn't
because I'm with you,
if that's what you're thinking.
You transported members of
the Church of Terra to Earth,
isn't that right?
[KONEV]
Yes, sir.
Considering the dangers
of carrying them
through a battlefield,
I hear the
resulting gains
were hardly worth it.
Is that the reason
you seem so displeased?
[KONEV chuckles]
Maybe.
[RUBINSKY] Incidentally, what do
you think about the Terraists?
[KONEV]
I'm not quite sure.
But in terms of
religion in general,
I think poor people
believing God to be fair
and just seems like
an obvious contradiction.
It's because God is biased that
the poverty-stricken exist.
Interesting thought.
I take it you don't
believe in God, then?
Nope, not even in the slightest.
Whoever came up with
the concept of God
was the greatest con
artist in history.
I only admire
that person's imagination
and business sense.
From ancient to current times,
the wealthiest ones
in every nation have
always been nobles,
landowners, and
religious organizations.
That's certainly
a fascinating viewpoint.
Is it your own original one, or
have you adopted someone else's?
The latter.
I heard most of it
when I was a child.
It was 16 or 17 years ago
when I was traveling
from planet to planet
with my father.
One day,
I met another boy who lived
in similar circumstances.
He was two years older than me,
very smart for his age,
and spent most of
his time thinking.
All those were
things he said to me.
Oh? What was
this philosopher's name?
It was Yang Wen-li.
I hear he's now found work
in the hopeless field
of military service.
A free man such
as myself can't help but pity
the poor fellow.
Captain Boris Konev.
[KONEV]
Yes, sir?
The government of
the Dominion of Fezzan
would like to delegate
a momentous duty to you.
[KONEV]
What?
[MARINESK]
Hey.
We got a notice from
the energy agency earlier.
They said we'd never
have to worry about fuel
for the Berezka again.
What kind of magic
did you use to pull that off?
[KONEV] Just sold myself
to the government.
They're sending me
to the Free Planets Alliance
as some sort of
intelligence officer.
[MARINESK]
Oh.
[KONEV] You know, the one
thing the Konev family was
most proud of was
that we've produced
no criminals nor
bureaucrats in 200 years!
We're free citizens! Free!
And now they want me
to be a spy, of all things!
That's both of those at once!
[MARINESK] Wasn't it
"Intelligence Officer"?
Not "spy"?
Changing the name
doesn't fix anything!
If you just called
cancer a cold,
would that mean
that it's not cancer?
If you got bit by
a lion and called it a mouse,
would you bleed any less?
They already looked into it
and knew I'd met Yang Wen-li
before I even mentioned it.
What a joke!
Maybe I should just contact Yang
and tell him about all this.
[MARINESK]
I don't think that'll work.
They'll have eyes
on you at all times.
They'll watch what you do
and punish you if necessary.
That damn Black Fox
probably thinks he's doing me
a favor by giving me this
cushy government position.
Fine, then. Let him.
He can keep on
believing that for now.
[KONEV]
Tch! Damn that Rubinsky!
I'm going to take him
down one day!
[MARINESK]
What are you, a child?
[NARRATOR] Next time on
Legend of the Galactic Heroes:
Die Neue These: Episode 22.
"The Fall of Goldenbaum."