I am the one pushin' on ahead
just like you, yeah yeah
Won't you please hear me now
and give a name to
the demon in the desert
You can't help
but clench your teeth
As your heart starts
to tremble from the heat
Now stop it
It'll only bring destruction
Let's do it!
I killed an angel
The time has come
to stand and be strong
It's a sad history
hidden in a big story
That is the mystery
There's no way now of knowin'
Knowin' about what
tomorrow holds for me
So I just keep moving on
Living till the moment's gone
Forever just me
My mission
Something bit me!
Die...!
It's jammed!
Dammit!
Huh?
Did I do that?
I just saved your
ass Desert Punk.
What...?
Who said that...? Hello?
Oh great.
Not you again!
You have a name right?
What is it?
It's Kosuna!
Am I that forgettable?!
You're saying, you didn't
see me following you...?
You gotta be
completely worn out,
I wasn't trying to dodge you.
After all you did almost die
out here in the desert, master.
And then just to make
everything worse...
after collapsing you were saved
by your long time loser rivals
the sleezy Machinegun Brothers.
Aren't you well informed?
Of course.
I know all about my master.
Which isn't gonna be me!
So why don't you
just scurry on home?!
Not a chance!
I'll follow you wherever you go
to prove my unflinching loyalty!
Why the hell do you want
to be my apprentice anyway?
Well that's simple!
I want to become
stronger than any man,
and more beautiful than
any woman known to man.
I want to be intelligent
and quick-witted
and destroy all the
bad guys on the earth!
Someday I'll be the prettiest
and mightiest chick in
the Great Kanto Desert!
No one'll screw with me!
It's great...
I can picture myself...
gorgeous.
Hey hold up!
Wait for me, master!
How's it goin' buddy...
I heard you had it kinda rough.
Feeling any better now?
Hey Desert Punk!
Get a little sand caught
in your helmet?
Hey kid, life's long,
hard and tough.
You're bound to
get into trouble...
But don't get all
down on yourself
just because you keeled over.
That's right...!
I heard you almost
died in the desert!
Let's go.
I don't want to
catch his "suckiness".
You're so famous!
Everyone in this town knows you!
Why me?!
You talking about
that poor wash-up?
That's right.
And we're the ones
who saved his dumb ass!
It was so pitiful!
You should have seen it!
When he saw us approaching him
he started
crying like a baby
and yelling, "I'm
saved! I'm saved!"
Damnit Haru!
So you're the one
spreading unjustified claims
about my personal
character around town!
I'm gonna take
this outta your ass!
But he's a mercenary.
I know, and that's what
makes it so damn funny...
If the guy had
any sense of shame
he'd never show his
face again in this town.
What a loser.
The villagers who hired him
to protect them were
disgusted by him...
Then he needed us to save him.
You bastards.
Quit spreading these
dirty lies about me
before you really piss me off!
What the hell do you
find so funny huh?!
I would have been fine out
there if I were by myself!
Look me in the eye DP!
What a pansy!
Loser!
I've had prettier
things look at me before.
Whoa... You must be
completely embarrassed.
Shut it.
Well that's not nice...
But what about me--
Well if it isn't Kanta.
Huh?
I heard you had a bad week...
But... it's good to see
you on your feet again.
Ha. Very funny Mizu. Jackass.
Seriously I envy you Kanta...
I'd give anything to
live a life of adventure
like your own with
the guns and the fighting.
No way.
Please don't get
into anything dangerous.
Back off!
My Mizu doesn't
want you that close.
There's no law that
says my Mizu's all yours,
so get it through
your thick skull, girl!
Now, now girls...
Let's try to get along
with each other okay.
I'm sure I'll
see you later Kanta.
And you better be ready
with some good
stories cause I'm all ears.
Who's the pretty boy?
The girls seem
to really like him.
Yeah he's the man.
Why's that?
Just look at him.
He's twenty-five and unemployed.
I don't think
I've ever seen him
with less than five
girls clinging to him.
His nickname is
the Harem Prince.
He's just surrounded by
easy chicks twenty-four seven.
Ugh...! That's nasty!
What the hell do you know?!
The chance to live each day
in pure bliss surrounded
by beautiful bouncing breasts.
Isn't that the ultimate
dream of every red-blooded man?
I can see it now.
You're nuts.
Whatever.
What is a man?
A man should
sweat when he works
and fight to protect
his family from the dangers
of the desert
environment and his enemies.
He should battle for his food
and carry it home on his back.
I'm glistening with man grease.
That's a man...
Yes... A truely manly man.
Well... good luck finding him.
I need to get back in shape.
I'm nowhere near my top form,
and I have to show those jerks
that made fun of
me what I'm made of.
If only I had Mizu's life.
Enough about you.
What about me?
Look if you make me your
apprentice you'll always,
have back up and I'll
even pick up after you.
I wouldn't mind if you were
stacked like Mizu's girlfriends.
But who in their
right mind would want
a pink-haired dumbbell
as their apprentice?
What?
I think it's time
I showed you something.
Whoa! Creepy!
Keep your clothes on!
That kinda thing's illegal!
But this ain't!
Holy taintstankles!
Who's the Holly Hotass?!
My mom.
You serious?
You following me yet?
I am her daughter...
which means that
I am the lucky one
to have inherited
her amazing genes...
I'm gonna look pretty
good when I get older.
Take a look and call me a liar.
Fine. I'll give you one shot!
Listen to the hand
for today's specials.
Eight legs for
the price of four!
Say...
What did you mean when you
said you'd give me a shot?
Uhh.
Come on, tell me?
Desert Punk?
Desert Punk!
Hey, what are you doing
over here master...? I...
It's settled.
Huh?
Oh, so this the kid...?
She's a bit on the...
scrawny side but I...
I got some work.
What's this...
I'm not feeling 100% yet,
so you can cover for
me until I'm up to par.
Got that? It's a golf term.
Let's see.
I'll start you off on
a simple job for ole Hash.
Wa-Wa-Wait a minute.
This won't work.
I want to become a
mercenary not a day laborer.
Put a sock in it!
You said you wanted to be
my apprentice, didn't you?
Yeah.
You said you'd do
whatever I said, right?
Yes!
In that case...
The job of a mercenary
is the most grueling job
in the entire desert.
It's also sought after
more than any other job.
So, how you do
today will determine
whether or not I accept
you as my apprentice.
I see where you're going
with this and I'm game!
You're gonna be
so impressed with me!
I am so freakin' psyched!
We'll see.
Oh I can't take
any more of this.
Thanks...
Damn septic tank's
been broken for a week.
I assumed that was the case.
Say...
Could I ask you to
deliver something for me?
Umm well...
Are you saying
you don't want to?
Because in my
experience mercenaries
will do just about
anything for a small price.
Fine, I'll do it!
Now this is the life.
I should have
gotten an apprentice
a long freakin' time ago.
I think I have
it all figured out.
The reason I
haven't had any luck
with women is simple.
They've all been
too damn independent
and mature for
someone like me.
But this time I'll
take that worthless piece
who's neither a man
nor a woman at this point...
and whip her body, mind,
and spirit into
the perfect specimen.
Oh Kanta you know
how to work it so good.
I'll turn her
into the best damned
mercenary's assistant
ever possibly imagined.
No touching the candy.
Sorry.
I'm so excited.
It's like that
tiny broad is gonna
be my own science experiment.
Please Mizu kiss me next...!
Kiss me kiss me
kiss me... please Mizu.
There's plenty
of me to go around.
Small time...
That is small time
Mizu... I have a plan.
I'll start experimenting,
first with the kid
and then I'll gather
all of the perfect broads
I've created over the
years... then I'll do it...
Build a boobie
amusement park just
for my own pleasure!
Delivery...
Delivery... Delivery!
Yes.
Oh! I have a delivery
for you from some Hash guy.
Hello... Have
you seen my pills...?
I think I dropped
them in the toilet.
I can't even
see what I'm doing.
Hey kid! Hurry up!
I ain't got all day!
Alright...
This will be the
perfect job for me.
Hurry up and draw
some customers here.
Yes sir!
Come one, come all.
It's a sale-e-bration!
Get forty percent
off any item here
at the newly
renovated Mushiya Store!
Your voice is too soft.
'Kay...
We've got forty
percent off every item!
Louder.
Forty percent off every item!
Please come over
here and buy something!
You're gonna
have to speak louder.
But there are
no customers around.
The streets are empty.
That's why you
gotta be louder...
To bring them to you!
It's a sale-e-bration!
Come check out
items forty percent off!
He even remodeled
the store so you
stop lollygagging and
buy something, dammit!
What?
I can't take it anymore!
It's so embarrassing.
What are you doing Kosuna?
Master, I can't-- I don't...
Look girly...
If you want to be
a mercenary you have
to do whatever's necessary.
I know that...
but I want to
help you fight bandits
and run guns
not clean chimneys
and scream at empty streets.
Kosuna... Do you
know why I was able
to defeat the
Shimmer Sniper... Do you?
No.
Because I am...
the Demon of the Desert.
That entire day he was
in a better position than me.
But I survived
that fight because of
the skills I've
acquired over the years.
Now granted
he was a damn good
sharpshooter,
better than me...
And he probably had a
hell of a lot more training...
But that was the
only advantage he had.
See...?!
Doing battle is the
same as going through life.
Conditions change from minute
to minute and you
have to be prepared
for events you
can't even predict.
You need to be able to read
each situation
with a rational mind.
Be clear in your decisions
and take action in an instant.
None of this is possible
without pure self-confidence
and that only
comes from experience.
To hone your abilities,
you need to experience
everything you can
no matter how crummy the job is.
And the only
profession that allows you
to make money while doing
this is mercenary work.
So you see... I am the balls.
You're amazing. A king!
I promise I'll
work as hard as I can
from now on without complaint.
Just remember
to learn something
valuable in, all that you do.
Yes sir!
Sweet...!
Now I get to blow all
the money she made for me!
Hey there Kanta.
Yo. I'm here to pick
up Kosuna's earnings.
Right, right.
Alright! I'm gonna
get so hammered tonight!
Here you go.
What is that?
The bill.
Huh?
I took care of the damages,
so just reimburse me.
What the... hell?
I'm gonna kill her!
That girl doesn't
have what it takes, Punk.
She spilled human
waste on a client...
she fell and re-covered
a chimney in soot...
She destroyed every
item she tried to deliver...
It was a total mess.
So the rumors I've
been hearing are true?
That's right...
It was all a lie...
Desert Punk is
nothing but a sham.
A two-timing hackjob.
You know I gave her those jobs
because you recommended her.
And I let my clients know that.
And after that
incident in the desert,
your credibility has
already taken a nose dive.
I hope you have a plan
for digging yourself out
of this hole
'cause it's a deep one.
Where is she?
If she's walking the
Campbell's Green Gordion beetle
then she should be close by.
That looks like a campfire.
Smells nice.
What's wrong?!
What the hell are you doing?!
Eating... I was
freaking starving here.
But... that beetle
is not for eating...
Oh, dammit.
This thing was a pet, stupid!
Mrs. Campbell loved it
more than her own children!
It's an endangered
species for crying out loud!
Who in the hell
keeps a bug as a pet?
How was I supposed to
know not to eat the thing...
You never told me.
You should know all
rich people are crazy!
You're lucky I don't just...
Don't... please don't ah oh...
be gentle... eh...
not in the face...
don't... ow... oh
Mrs. Campbell.
Oh my sweet Tama.
Did you enjoy your walk?
Come give mommy a kiss.
What, what's wrong?
We, had, a problem.
Just give her
to me. How dare you.
You...! What did you do
to my Tama you
ugly little bastard!
It was an accident. I swear!
Do you have any idea...
I want to sock this rich
snot in the face right now,
but I have to be patient.
Think long term Kanta.
How do you plan on making
up for this neglect, huh?
I knew I shouldn't
have trusted you
after I heard about what
happened to you in the desert.
So it looks like I'm
right back to where I started.
Swimming in debt.
My buddy.
What's happening Kanta?
Huh?
Whatcha doing big guy?
Getting in touch
with your inner self?
Enjoying the sunset...
And... doing a little
of what you mentioned.
That's cool.
My friend...
that is a truly
beautiful sight.
Yes it is...
So tell me Mizu
why are you so blue?
And what happened
to your pretty face?
About that...
What the...?!
I'm gonna kill you and then
myself you cheatin' bastard!
Wait stop!
I was just a
conquest for you wasn't I?
Yeah me too.
What about me?
I loved you.
Wait... Hold on...
Let me explain, ladies...
I love you all equally.
I thought I could get away
with loving all my
girls at the same time...
but women don't
work like that.
Wow, they really jacked you up.
You don't know the half of it.
Take it easy, Kanta.
Yeah you too. Good luck.
I guess ...
I'm not the only
one out there...
with problems to handle.
Ah screw it...
I suppose I'm gonna have
to work that much harder.
In order to reach my dreams
of building a
boobie amusment park.
There they are.
Not long after
that sunset a new pair
was spotted in
the Great Kanto Desert.
Listen. Attack when
I give the signal.
You got it, master.
It was Desert Punk and
his new apprentice, Kosuna.
But there wasn't
an ounce of respect
or trust between them.
Only selfishness and greed kept
these two working together.
May these two unfortunate souls
find happiness in their misery.
Let's go Kosuna!
Right behind ya!
You are the most pathetic
sidekick I've ever laid eyes on.
I just want you
to know that next time
you think you're a badass.
Can you hear me?
Can you talk? Hello?
Start with one circle
Add one more circle
Then add one more big circle
Then a raincoat
blowing in the wind
It's actually a cape.
Whoa, don't forget
about the sunshade now
His heart is the
blackest in the desert.
His heart is black.
Shotgun is what he's gonna use
And then you've got
yourself a Sunabozu
He's on the run again
On the run again.
Just one more day and you'll see
He's got a job.
He won't stop
till tomorrow comes
He won't stop until
he gets the girl.
Until he gets the girl.
Get that girl!
Risking your life is
what you do, what you do
It's what you do
Yo! Desert Punk here.
Sorry there were no
gnugens this time around.
Don't worry, Master!
We flat-chested girls have
a flavor all to ourselves!
I bet it tastes awful!
Like you'd know!
Next time on Desert Punk,
"A Dog in Heat!"
If you miss it
your boobs will deflate!