I am the one pushin' on ahead
just like you, yeah yeah
Won't you please hear me now
and give a name to
the demon in the desert
You can't help
but clench your teeth
As your heart starts
to tremble from the heat
Now stop it
It'll only bring destruction
Let's do it!
I killed an angel
The time has come
to stand and be strong
It's a sad history
hidden in a big story
That is the mystery
There's no way now of knowin'
Knowin' about what
tomorrow holds for me
So I just keep moving on
Living till the moment's gone
Forever just me
My mission
Man this job is boring.
Tell me about it. Us
newbies get the crap work.
I told my folks
I would make it big
when I left home,
and now I'm stuck out here
and haven't even shot my weapon.
What's up?
I think I saw a kid.
A kid? Are you sure about that?
We're way far out.
This is the last place
I'd expect to see a kid.
No man, I'm serious.
Check it out.
See! There it was again!
Hold up!
You're not supposed
to leave your post!
Idiot.
How much longer
do we have to wait?
Easy.
Have some patience.
No, kidding.
By the time the
sun rises tomorrow
we'll have more money
than we'll know what to do with.
What's going on?!
Oh... Sorry...
Did we wake you Mr. Shimada?
Isn't it about time
you guys changed guards?
Right. We lost track of time.
We'll get on that right away.
Come on guys, let's punch
it up a bit, let's move!
I'm moving, I'm moving.
So, why isn't
she eating anything?
Don't know. She
won't even look at it.
We warmed it up and everything.
I put the mask back on
her just to keep her quiet.
Guess she's not a big fan
of cookies, butter,
and dog food.
Well, she can
starve for all I care.
If she continues to
refuse I could always
shove the food down her throat.
Just leave her be.
Come morning when
our client arrives
this little babysitting
job will be over.
This brat is gonna make us
some serious money ain't she?
I figure each
of us will get more
than an entire year's
salary out of this, huh?
Don't bother speculating
on how much you're gonna get.
It'll only bring
you disappointment.
We do the job
we're hired to do...
and that's all you should
concern yourself with.
Somebody! Come quick!
Stay here and watch the girl.
What the--?!
Who could have done this?
Well, are they both alive?
Yeah. They're just
knocked out pretty good.
This is strange.
Huh?
Whoever did this could
have just killed them.
Why put them
on display like this?
What purpose does it serve?
Oh no it's about the girl!
We're dealing with a pro guys.
Come on. Get up.
I had guards placed
all over this floor.
How did he...
Sorry, sir.
I never even saw it,
I was attacked from above.
Above?
Oh, I see.
Send out an alert.
Seal all the exits.
We can't let them get away.
Yes, sir!
You three come with me.
We're going on a rat hunt
boys so bring your A game.
It's a real ballsy
move to steal a mark
from professional kidnappers...
This guy has no idea
who he's dealing with.
That was close.
I recognize that guy.
He's the legendary
Night Mist, the best,
or at least most professional,
kidnapper in the world.
And that guy's quick so
I gotta be one step ahead.
Stop wiggling kid.
Kosuna can you
hear me? Kosuna? Pick up!
Yeah. Loud and clear.
The situation has changed.
Switch our strategy from
Cyclone to Hurricane. Copy?
What? I just finished
setting up Cyclone!
Stop complaining and just do it!
Fine. Right away sir.
Calm down. It's gonna
be all right kid.
You must have
been pretty scared, huh?
The nerve of
those guys tying up
a helpless child like
this. You poor thing.
You're lucky I
found you in time.
Get away!
What's wrong?
Mind your own business, pal.
Mind my own what?!
I bet my daddy asked
you to rescue me...
Figures he can't do it himself.
Yeah, uh, he hired me.
I hope you're careful with me
because I don't want to
get caught in the crossfire
of a gunfight between
you macho boys.
If my daddy had
just paid the ransom
this would all be over with
and I'd be at home with my toys.
But...
Oh no! My favorite dress!
Look you got it
all dirtied up...!
What are you going
to do about it, huh?
It was a one of a kind!
What am I going to do
about it, I'm rescuing you?!
I assume we're going to have
to start walking
after this right...?
Of course we--
Well I'll have you know
that I don't like to walk...
What are you nuts?
And I'm hungry too and I assume
you have some food for me.
You're starting
to drive me crazy!
Don't you know how to listen
when someone's talking?!
I would think you'd
act a little nicer
to someone who's
trying to save your life.
But what do I know?
Look little girl.
This is not a simple
snatch-and-grab kidnap
for ransom case okay?
There's a lot
more to it than that.
What are you talking about?
These guys are professionals
that were hired to kidnap you.
They're not thugs
looking for a quick buck.
But I don't understand.
I'm just an innocent,
fragile, little girl.
Okay.
Your father recently
used some, questionable
if not unethical, tactics
to aid in the demise
of a rival company. Got it?
Now the person
that hired these guys
to kidnap you is probably
the owner of that company.
Um, whatever you say.
In other words their
goal is not money.
It's a grudge. It's malice.
Their goal is to
make your father suffer
in the worst possible way,
which is why you're here now.
Geez! You just don't
get it do you?!
Listen to me. Okay?
What I'm saying
is paying the ransom
doesn't mean you're going
to go home safe and sound.
Is, that a fact?
Yes. Usually they
would just take the ransom
and then kill you anyway.
You get off lucky
if they just kill you.
However more often than not,
they'll force you to
satisfy the desires of fat,
sweaty, stanked-out men
and trust me little girl,
death is a sweet
release in comparison.
I got her scared.
Good, that should
keep her in line.
Would the fat man want me
because he thinks I'm cute?
I knew it...
I know I shouldn't
point it out myself,
but I'm a pretty girl
that all the boys want
to be with, aren't I?!
Give me a break.
It must be because I've
been raised so well...
Even criminals can see it...
I'll grow up to be a great
wife and an excellent mother.
I don't believe
this wretched kid!
Look we have
to start running now
or we'll be throat
deep in trouble! Got it?
Sure I got it but,
my conditions are no pain,
no dirt, and no
running. Got that?
Why did I take this job?
Time to go. They found us.
They did?
Shut up and run.
We have to move!
Hold on!
I don't think it's on... hey!
We found them. Thirteenth
floor section B.
Okay let everyone know
we're closing in on the rat.
Stay focused out there.
Copy that.
Huh, this is
starting to get fun...
It's been awhile since
I've felt such a rush.
Impressive.
They're approaching
on all sides.
Waiting patiently, no rushing,
slowly closing in on us.
Hey.
There's no hesitation.
Hello!
They must know this
building inside and out.
Mister!
This isn't going to be easy.
They have a solid
advantage from every position.
Listen to me!
What is it?!
I'm really tired.
Tired? We haven't even
walked five minutes yet.
I can't take another step.
Come on kid. Enough
with the games already.
Shut up kid!
You'll give away our position!
I'm dirty and I'm hungry.
She's gonna blow
this whole operation!
I want to go home
and see my daddy!
I'd give anything for a
tranquilizer dart right now
but even then my exits
are all blocked... Kosuna.
Do you read me?
Yes, Master.
I read you.
What's going on?
Well I can honestly say that
since we teamed up
this is the first time
I've found you to
be an obedient kid.
Okay...?
Anyways I need you to
drop the Hurricane strategy.
We're moving right
into Monsoon now.
We're changing again?
I was almost finished!
I don't care!
You have to be
ready to change strategies
at a moment's notice
depending on the situation.
Now go!
Come on kid let's get moving...
Hello?
What is it?
You're not going to
throw another fit are you?
I have to use the facilities.
What?
Speak up kid.
I said, I need to...
Volume! I can't hear a word.
Stop trying to
embarrass me you ass!
I have to pee real bad!
That's what I was saying!
Oh, you have to pee.
Why didn't you just
say that in the first place?
You're so mean.
Just hold it for now.
I can't hold it!
Then just go right
there. I'll keep watch.
I need privacy!
You're unbelievable!
I'm gonna go in that
dark corner over there.
Wait. It's too
dangerous to be by yourself.
If you look I'll tell my
dad you're a creepy pervert!
She will make a great bitch.
What's taking her so long?
I should check
on her. No I can't.
If she thinks I'm peeking
and has another one of
her tantrums the kidnappers
will find us for sure.
Plus I don't want
any rumors flying around
that I spied on a little
girl going to the toilet.
Who knows what Junko
or the Machinegun
Brothers would think of that.
Wait a sec...
Kosuna come in.
Yeah what is it?
Wait you're not changing
the strategy again are you?
No I just wanted
to ask you something.
Okay, shoot.
It's a weird
question but how long
does it usually
take for a girl to pee?
These girls will
be the end of me.
No of course
that's not the case.
I'm not at all interested
in that type of thing.
But given the situation
I'm in I have no other choice.
The kid's simply taking
too long to come back
and I'm worried,
worried, nothing more.
I just need to
check for her safety.
So I'm not a pervert.
No I'm not a pervert.
Not a pervert. Not a pervert.
What is taking her so long?
Hey kid.
I'm not trying to be weird.
I just need to
check that you're okay.
It's in my contract
with your father
that I return you
in perfect condition.
Are you listening to me? Hello?
Well, look who it is.
Tell me, what kind
of sick bastard gets off
watching little
girls tinkle. Huh?
Looks like
you're cornered buddy.
Sucks for you
because Mr. Shimada
knows this building
like the back of his hand.
There's no use in running
because we'll know
exactly where you're going.
So without getting too close
you were following me,
waiting for the
kid and I to separate?
Duh! This young lady
is a very valuable
source of cash for us.
We couldn't risk her
safety in a gun battle.
Now it's about
time we got you back
for that stunt
you pulled earlier.
The choice is yours.
Either you can take a beating
and then fall to
your death, or you can take
a beating and fall
to your death, huh.
Why don't you do us
a favor and just jump.
There are five of them.
The odds are against me.
They know every
corner of this complex,
so if I decide to run they'll
probably find me right away.
Let's see, decisions decisions.
Ah what the hell.
Hey what are you doing?!
What the--?
Damn! He blew out
our night goggle things!
I can't see anything!
Let's go princess!
Damn. Find them!
Hold on!
I don't like this!
It's dark and scary!
And it smells like crotch
rot! No, this is so freaky!
Shut up! It's not that bad.
You're sick!
Why are you kicking me?!
No one's allowed
to touch me there!
My daddy told me...
Found them!
There in here.
You gave us away!
Watch your fire!
Your gonna hit the kid!
Ow that hurt.
Way to go genius!
Now my hair is full
of dust thanks to you!
And the way you
saved me back there.
What was that all about?
You were dragging
me around like a caveman!
What if my face had
gotten all scratched up?
What would you have done then?
Probably nothing!
I hope you realize that my face
is worth a heck of
a lot more than yours...!
I bet your face
is so ugly you have
to wear that
helmet all the time
when you're in
public so you don't scare
the children that
think you're some sort of...
You're only pretty
because your father
is so rich he probably
bought you a new face.
I knew it!
If my daddy heard you say
that he would be
really angry with you.
Then what do say
we don't tell Daddy.
Great, I hear them,
they caught up with us again.
We can't use the
ventilation ducts anymore...
Kosuna, come in.
I'm here.
Want to talk about going
to the bathroom again?
No! It's about the game plan.
Oh then don't you worry, sir.
I'm carrying out the
Monsoon Strategy as we speak.
Cancel Monsoon.
Focus all of your
attention on Phoenix.
Are you doing this on purpose?
Shut up and listen!
Phoenix Strategy now! Go!
Okay.
There! Don't let
them get away...!
We found them sir.
He went your way!
Get in front of them!
This is the checkmate... pal.
He was smarter
than I anticipated.
But making a move
like this is suicide...
This guy must be
just a lucky amateur.
I guess he doesn't realize
that by running upwards
in that part of the
building he's cutting off
his own escape route.
Unless he's thinking...
I'm done. I can't go on!
Cut the crap already!
You want to be
that greasy old fat
man's love child forever?
But I can't
help it! I'm so tired!
This way!
Roughly ten enemies. Perfect.
Get on.
Smoke bomb!
Don't stop! Keep moving!
No, wait! Stay there!
We've got them cornered!
Those with head in
clouds fall down hole.
We finally made it.
Well, where are we going now?
Kosuna! Where are you?
You better be prepared!
Well look who it is.
I had a hunch it
was you Desert Punk.
You're not half bad
for a low life mercenary.
You're a mercenary?!
Well that's just great!
No wonder you got caught.
Daddy should
have spent a lot more
and gotten a
real man for the job!
You're pathetic!
It's nice to meet you.
I've heard many tales about
the legend of Night Mist
and here I stand before you.
It's too bad we had to meet
under these circumstances.
Unfortunately I need
to cut this meeting short.
Yeah well...
Drop your guns or your cash cow
here gets a bullet in her brain.
Desert Punk,
think this one through.
She's a valuable
commodity alive, right?
If you don't want her dead
then I suggest you help me.
Time's a tickin'
boys, make your choice.
Wait just a minute.
You can't shoot me!
My daddy would have
you killed if you did that!
Shut your sloppy pie
hole you little brat!
I'll just tell him
I didn't get here in time.
He won't know the difference.
You're crazy!
I'll be sure to collect my fee
though whether
you're dead or alive!
That's one sick puppy.
You're just like
your reputation says...
A cunning, cowardly,
worthless waste of human flesh.
Say what you will.
If you want to
kill the girl go ahead.
What?
It doesn't matter to us
if the girl lives or dies.
It doesn't affect
our business too much.
Sure we won't get as
much for delivering a corpse,
but it would be worth
the loss to see you fail.
I refuse to let you
have your way Desert Punk.
You will die here today.
Is that right?
What if I drop a
bomb and vaporize her?!
How would that work out?!
Kosuna! You're late!
Huh?
Whoops.
So you had an accomplice!
Kosuna! Phoenix strategy! Go!
Roger dodger!
What in the hell do
you think your doing?!
Isn't this a little
much for Phoenix?
Whatta ya mean?
I did exactly as you told me.
Two sticks of TNT at
all ten support fixtures.
You idiot!
That's the Tornado Plan!
I told you to set
up Phoenix! Phoenix!
That was a close one...!
Saved at the last second!
You mercenaries
are more prepared
than I took you
for, having a parachute
on your back the whole time.
Yeah that's fine and dandy
but it looks like we
picked up an extra passenger.
We're overloaded, Master!
We're losing altitude fast!
We're what?!
Would you let go of my leg!
There's only room
for three on this ride!
Shut up you reckless bastard!
I can't believe I didn't
know you were
working with a partner.
First class
mercenaries like myself
are always three steps
ahead of frauds like you.
Don't laugh too soon!
You don't have a
check in your hand yet!
Face it, you lost!
Get rid of that guy Master!
If I'm going down
I'm taking you with me!
Get off me!
You bunch of morons!
We're all going to die.
Master!
I did it!
We're floating again!
In one of the most unorthodox
and selfish escapes
in recent history,
the little girl
in effect freed herself
from her kidnapper...
at her savior's expense.
Are you feeling
any better Master?
About the reward
from the last job,
I took my share
before I paid off
some of your outstanding debts.
It's not much
but here's what's left.
I'm gonna go shopping!
Hope you feel better! See ya!
Start with one circle
Add one more circle
Then add one more big circle
Then a raincoat
blowing in the wind
It's actually a cape.
Whoa, don't forget
about the sunshade now
His heart is the
blackest in the desert.
His heart is black.
Shotgun is what he's gonna use
And then you've got
yourself a Sunabozu
He's on the run again
On the run again.
Just one more day and you'll see
He's got a job.
He won't stop
till tomorrow comes
He won't stop until
he gets the girl.
Until he gets the girl.
Get that girl!
Risking your life is
what you do, what you do
It's what you do
Yo! Desert Punk here.
What's with the
lack of boobies?!
Don't worry! I'll
be busty in five years!
Or better make
that ten just to be safe!
Oh whatever, I want boobs now!
Next on Desert Punk,
"Opposites Collide!"
If you miss it you
won't get no boobs!