I am the one pushin' on ahead
just like you, yeah yeah
Won't you please hear me now
and give a name to
the demon in the desert
You can't help
but clench your teeth
As your heart starts
to tremble from the heat
Now stop it
It'll only bring destruction
Let's do it!
I killed an angel
The time has come
to stand and be strong
It's a sad history
hidden in a big story
That is the mystery
There's no way now of knowin'
Knowin' about what
tomorrow holds for me
So I just keep moving on
Living till the moment's gone
Forever just me
My mission
I'll pull the cart when
we get to the next village.
Dad... I'm fine.
Don't worry about it.
I'm sorry I'm not stronger.
Dad!
Are you okay? What happened?
I'm... I'm sorry Noriko...
You go on... without me.
Dad... You'll be fine.
You're acting ridiculous.
My daughter...
I'm here, dad.
Noriko...
Yes...? What do you need?
I love you--
No... No dad!
Dad!
Several centuries
after the collapse
of modern civilization...
This is the Great Kanto Desert.
This is a world of survival.
Here, justice is on the side
of whoever is left standing.
Some say the victor
in this wasteland
is a demon from the sand.
A phantom mercenary.
He is also known by
the name Desert Punk.
And one last move
for good measure!
Hold on pal!
His grandkids are gonna
feel that crack to the nuts...
Hell, I felt it.
You... You son of a bitch...
You're cold!
Cold I maybe, but I'm thorough.
This'd all be a lot
easier if that Junko chick
hadn't ganked me out of my cash.
But I gotta say,
that girl did have one
grade-A rack on her.
Whoa, whoa, enough, enough.
Geez If get tits on the brain
I can kiss that score
goodbye for good.
I tell you what though,
without women,
I'd have a much better
focus in my life.
From now on, I have
to be clear-headed.
Okay put your hands
up in the air now!
That's right! But do it slowly!
I said, hands up!
Don't make him
tell you again! Do it!
He's so scared
he can't even move!
Look, he's frozen in the sand!
He's just screwing around!
If that's who I think it is,
he's pretty damn ruthless,
even for a collector.
I've heard old
men in the villages
tell stories about his methods.
The way they tell it,
when he collects your money,
he collects your very soul.
Hey, why are you
just standing there?!
The way I understand it,
you want me to
show you my hands.
Yeah... That's right.
Hands in the air,
and we might just
let you walk out of here.
What the hell is this stuff?!
It hurts!
Thread...? You serious?
I've shown you my
hands like you asked.
What's next?
Hot! Hot! Ouch! Ouch!
Kill us!
You can't make us return
to the village like this!
We'll never live this down!
Please kill us!
Don't make us go back!
My brothers will tear me apart!
It'll be worse than death!
Is that so?
Forget it! We'll just
steal some pants!
Jackasses.
I sure didn't have to see
those things dangling like that.
When those old guys
said you took souls,
they must've meant "pride".
Some things get twisted as
they get passed on, I guess.
That was just for
wasting my time.
I knew someone was watching me.
I didn't realize it was the
famous Desert Punk, though.
Gotta hand it to you,
Rain Spider.
You got some good instincts.
I don't think we've
ever met formally.
No, but you have quite
the reputation in Kanto.
I feel like I already know you.
Aw, shucks.
Cut it out, big guy.
I've watched you work, now.
The skills of the
number one collector
in these parts are
no longer a secret.
Too bad I haven't
seen you in action.
I'd love to see how you prey on
the weak and the helpless.
Uh, well, if the opportunity
arises, bring it on.
Wait--
Some other time, maybe.
I have urgent
business elsewhere.
Oh, that's too bad.
Check you later.
Today I've come
across every loser
and blow-hard this
desert has to offer.
It's getting old.
You're earlier
than expected, kid.
Not by choice.
What job is up next?
Eh, Hold on a second.
I'll check the board.
Mommy, I'm still
really hungry...
Here it is... Atoll 22.
There's a man called Koike
living at 29-3, Bakshi Street.
The money he owes is past due
and collection is in order.
This request comes
from Akashio Financial.
All right... 29-3... Uh...
29-3 is... here?
Man, it's a freakin'
dump! What a crapshack!
Knock, knock!
I'm, uh, looking for
some old dude named Koike.
Anyone here?
Hi...
I had no idea you
knew old Koike here.
None of my friends are
that ugly or that damn poor.
But if I'm here to see this guy
and Rain Spider is here
to see this guy then--
I'm here to collect of course.
Koike took a loan out
from Oshio Financial
in the South Oasis and
today is the repayment date.
Unfortunately,
as is usually the case,
Koike doesn't seem to
have the money on him.
Go figure.
What a bunch of crap.
My luck sucks this week.
I have one guess as
to what kind of business
you have with
our elderly friend.
You broke old bastard!
You took money out
from two loan companies
at the same time?!
I want all of the money you owe
Akashio Financial right now!
Wait, hold on!
The Akashio loan
is way past due!
You owe money in
the south and the west!
That's pretty damn ballsy.
Now reach inside your pockets
and find it
somewhere inside of you
to give back what
you were given!
Give it back!
Hey! I was here first!
I have dibs on this guy!
Dibs?
You're talking like
there're rules to this!
I need that cash!
Oh no, you don't!
You're tough
for a little squirt!
You're not getting
anything today!
You wanna bet?!
I'll turn this house
over until I find the cash.
Oh, shut up!
He's right.
There's not a damn thing here.
And this place stinks.
It stinks bad.
I'm sorry, but with
my failing health,
I can't work...
No one will
hire me for anything.
Let me ask you something, Koike.
In this lawless hellhole
of an existence,
do you know why the
loan sharks thrive as they do?
N-No...
Because of people
like us. Collectors.
No matter what injuries
we may sustain,
no matter what kind
of resistance we face,
we will always,
and I mean always,
find the debtor
and capture him alive.
That is the way
of a professional.
Then we use whatever
means necessary
to get the debt paid.
I have a reputation
for finishing jobs!
You can be as old or
as sick as you want,
my job stays the same!
I just want the damn money!
Dad?
What a sweet-looking chick!
I'd like to split
her like lumber.
What's going on...?
What are you doing to my father?
So you're the only one working
and bringing in the money.
Must be hard
supporting a sick man.
Forgive me... It's my fault.
I knew the payment was due.
I don't see how someone like you
could earn the kind of
money needed to pay this debt.
You're right.
But I am trying
as hard as I can.
I worked hard and found a
job at a printing company.
But when the owner was
killed by a gang of thugs...
and the deadline for
the payment was looming,
I had to take any job.
But lugging around loads
was too much for
a woman like me.
The men were much more able.
So I looked into something
I could do on my own.
But I failed at
that, too. I failed.
I've just... never
been good at anything!
I'm sorry Noriko...
But I am more proud of
you than I have ever been.
Dad, you're going
to be all right...!
You've got to stop all this!
It's not your
fault you got sick!
It's all my fault dear.
Even the loss of your mother...
Dad, enough of this, okay...
You promised we'd
never speak of that.
My, Noriko...
You know I love you Dad...
We're both doing our best.
Not now... We have guests.
You can't just bawl up a storm
in front of strangers.
Oh, all right.
You know, Akashio Financial
might swing another
ten days or so...
They... they might
be okay with that.
Are you sure?
Um... yeah. I mean sure.
What's your deal?!
Oh, nothing.
Liar!
You were thinking
what a wussy I am
for letting that chick
and her dad's weepiness
get under my skin.
Well...
You got another bright idea?
Cause there's nothing
in this house of any value!
We checked, remember?
I'm not so sure about that.
What about her?
Noriko...! No! Let her go!
What are you doing to her,
you freakin' jerk?!
Crap! Are you
all right old man?!
This young lady might be poor
and covered in dust,
but her beauty
and her kind-heartedness
are unmistakable.
Selling her could bring
in quite a load of cash.
You're right. I hadn't
even considered that.
No absolutely not!
Do you have ice water
in your veins?!
Probably.
Let me ask you a question.
How do you plan to
reclaim the debt?
The house is empty, as
you've shrewdly observed.
Only the girl has any value,
black market or otherwise.
How you are going to collect
without selling the girl is
a better question, I think.
You said yourself that
you always finish your jobs.
I still think it's wrong.
But go ahead and sell her...
On one condition...
I'm the buyer.
You sell her to me.
But I can't pay much.
You'll have to find
a way to take the rest
out of her father if you
want to pay back Oshio.
This is my final offer!
That's moronic.
It seems that our
time spent here talking...
is over!
Winner takes the girl.
Loser figures out a
different way to get the dough.
That's it. Sound like
a fair deal to you?
No objections here.
Don't think
I'll let this girl go
into the hands of some crazy,
fetish-prone mercenary
like you without a fight.
If you're done talking
we can get this started.
What's that all about?
Uh, looks like a fight.
It's like one of those
old fashioned duels.
And it's between Rain
Spider and Desert Punk!
No way. They'll destroy
everything around them!
If I'm not mistaken,
it's a fight
to decide who gets
Koike's daughter.
What?
Desert Punk and Rain Spider.
But elder...
Why are you here?
We cannot let these two fight...
If they do, our
entire village could be
leveled by their
fury and turmoil.
♪ No one knows
from where he comes ♪
♪ Flying briskly
across the sand ♪
♪ He soars without
sound through the night ♪
♪ Spreading fear
across the land ♪
♪ He flies
where no one goes ♪
♪ collecting what he can,
destroying foes. ♪
♪ And never facing death because
he wears a big damn mask ♪
♪ which saves his skin
from the scorching sun ♪
♪ The Demon of
the Desert. AKA... ♪
♪ Desert Punk.
Desert Punk. Desert Punk. ♪
They don't seem
like they're going to--
I'm not finished yet.
♪ Desert storms
of sand and glass ♪
♪ will bring you to your
knees as you beg for mercy. ♪
♪ And just like a storm, ♪
♪ the Rain Spider
won't give you a break. ♪
♪ He tracks his prey,
all careful and stuff. ♪
♪ hunting them down,
stealing their souls, ♪
♪ which he stomps
on with his boots ♪
♪ There's no escaping
this night rider ♪
♪ The evil Rain Spider! ♪
He kinda sucks, doesn't he?
Yeah... Pretty bad actually.
I know this guy has the
skills to really go at it.
But he basically uses
the same techniques as me.
Which means, my little tricks
probably won't work on him.
I'll have to find
a different angle.
He might be squatty,
but he didn't get his
reputation for nothing.
He's seen me in action, too,
which puts me behind
the eight ball a bit.
I'll have to try
something different.
This is going to be
one hell of a battle.
All right!
This is it!
Take that!
This blows.
You missed!
Yeah... it really does.
I've seen this kinda thing
a hundred times before.
And done better.
You've got a point.
I was so concerned with
watching for his tricks,
that I never expected to
find myself in a gun battle.
This is a waste of ammo!
I might as well be
shooting into the air!
Grandpa, you shouldn't
be out here walking around.
What would Grandma say?
Yoko, is lunch ready yet?
I'm hungry. I missed breakfast.
Of course,
I'll make you whatever.
We just have to
get you off your feet.
Where did you find a
rifle like that out here?
I brought it with me!
Just like you did with yours!
Eat this!
Shit!
Here's one for you!
Ah, no!
Suck my lead!
What happens when
we run out of ammo?
Will we fight
with swords then?
En garde!
The girl is mine!
No, she ain't!
All I hear from you
is bitch-bitch-bitch.
You're fighting with nothing!
Enough of this!
Your voice is making me crazy!
Now you loose, you tiny vermin!
You haven't laid
me out yet, jerk!
You'd better be ready
for that right now!
This is stupid. I'm going
to the bar for a drink.
Good idea.
Isn't it happy hour?
I'm gonna have a
sex on the beach.
You know, Spider.
Your punches are
losing some of their uh...
uh... punch...
Your legs look shaky.
How they feeling?
We got you where we
want you Rain Spider!
You're gonna pay for
what you did to us!
I found you Desert Punk!
You're gonna pay for
what you did to my boys!
All right, then--
What happened? You cool?
I gotta say...
you really are a badass.
I'd have to say
the same about you.
How bout we rest for a
while. Then we start again.
Sounds fine to me.
Two IOU's... They're mine.
That one guy, I just
had to look at sideways
and he folded.
Then the two of
them started fighting
just like we planned.
It was great.
I never knew why you always make
the repayment date
on mom's memorial day.
But today I think
I finally figured it out.
That's just like your mother
to watch out for us so well.
Dad... don't get
that tomato juice
on your clothes again.
It stains.
The promissory notes are burned.
Nothing but ashes left,
and we owe no money!
So... where are we going
to "borrow" our next round from?
Wherever it is, this time
you're buying me
a very nice dress.
I don't know dear.
We're on a very
tight budget as it is.
We can certainly afford
vodka for your tomato juice.
The Great Kanto Desert.
Here, justice is on the side
of whoever is left standing.
The losers are those
who cannot adapt
to the conditions.
Men, women, children,
the fools, the trash,
and the scorned live
by one creed... Survive.
Survival is expensive.
Start with one circle
Add one more circle
Then add one more big circle
Then a raincoat
blowing in the wind
It's actually a cape.
Whoa, don't forget
about the sunshade now
His heart is the
blackest in the desert.
His heart is black.
Shotgun is what he's gonna use
And then you've got
yourself a Sunabozu
He's on the run again
On the run again.
Just one more day and you'll see
He's got a job.
He won't stop
till tomorrow comes
He won't stop until
he gets the girl.
Until he gets the girl.
Get that girl!
Risking your life is
what you do, what you do
It's what you do
Yo. What's up?
I'm Desert Punk and
the next episode
has some nice tit action...
Wait. No titties?
Poor baby.
But I love boobs.
Oh, like you're gonna get any.
On the next Desert Punk,
"Fire Dragon Kong!"
If you miss it,
I won't pay what I owe.