Give it up, girly.
You don't have a chance
in hell of escaping me.
If we're done, I think Kosuna
and I will be heading back now.
I can't thank you enough
for all the hard
work you've put in...
You've done a great job
at earning that
reputation of yours.
I do what I can.
All the violence helps.
And somewhere along the
way you've managed to train a
damn good apprentice as well...
You should be quite proud
of yourself young Kosuna.
Oh, no. It was nothing.
I just watched over
Mitz most of the time.
It's about time she got into
guys who're more her own age.
It's about time you got
into guy's your own age.
Mitz, why you hiding
behind your dad?
You a little fairy now cause
you got babysat by a girl?
Oh I get it now!
Mitzy's gotta crush!
Nanny nanny boo boo!
I'd stop picking on him,
if I were you.
Remember last time...?
When you had to re-learn
how to pee standing up?
Yeah ... Uhhh... Yeah.
That sucked.
Don't wanna go there again.
We should do this
more often. Stay in touch.
Yeah, see ya.
And I'm paying for
dinner next time. I'm not.
That was so unreal!
I had no idea that
you had a master, too!
We all learn how
to shit from someone.
Anyone who says otherwise
is a friggin' liar.
And probably out to get you.
What I'm saying
is that your master
doesn't seem like he taught you.
He's so nice and... unassuming.
What have I told you
about big words?
They have no use in the
desert, I know. Sorry.
With Koid, what you
see is what you get.
He's a nice guy.
Yeah... He is.
Help!
Oh, those luxurious milk motels!
Bags that big can
only belong to Junko!
Let's say 'hi' with a squeeze!
Why can't you ever
recognize me by my face?
Probably cause the
ugly gets in the way.
I can't believe I found you!
What?
I went looking
for you in some town
and they said you
were out on a job.
I came as fast as I could.
I was so worried that
I couldn't find you, but I did!
This is a lifesaver!
What kind of a loser
do you think I am?!
Get off of me!
You cant just show up,
give me a brumpsky,
then expect me to
do whatever you want!
I deserve better
I deserve respect!
You're sounding
like a crazy man.
I sound crazy? You're crazy!
As far as I can recall,
nothing bad ever happened
between you and I.
I'll show you 'nothing bad'!
Did you forget all about that
stupid contract you signed?
Trapped in your hideout, she
used her wiley womanly ways.
This ring a bell?
I assume you're finished
with the job you
were doing out here.
And I talked with Mugenya.
He gave me something.
Here it is. Your new job.
My what now??!
That's a real Mugenya contract.
Rescue Junko Asagiri. ASAP.
And the job payment
is two million yen!
Whoa!
I thought that'd be a
fair pay for your services.
What kind of a mess
are you in this time?
I'm sorry?
This sounds like a crock.
Who would pay that kind
of cash just to save you?
Someone with low self-esteem?
Forget it!
What?
I wouldn't do anything for you,
even if it was you I had to do!
You have to listen, Kanta!
If you don't help me I'm going
to be forced into marriage!
No way!
WAY!
I just saw a glint
from something on
the top of that hill...
Sniper fire!
Master!
He's fine. Just a
little concussion.
He's coming.
Then we gotta get outta here.
Does this mean
that you'll help me?
That's not my call,
but we're leaving now.
But I've always thought
that you didn't like me.
I hate you! But I... I can't...
I'm not strong enough to
carry my Master by myself.
HUH...
If I agree to what you want,
he'll cut my head off
when he wakes up.
So, if you want help to get
Mr. Sniper off our backs,
I'm gonna need you to
hand over that contract.
Oh... So the brat's got
some brains in there.
She's still not willing
to throw in the towel.
What's that sound?!
My Kanta...
Come, to me!!
You have to listen, Kanta...!
If you don't help me I'm going
to be forced into marriage!
Junko!
POR-QUE JUNKOOOO!
PORQUE HABLO ESPANOL?!
Welcome to the
land of the living...
How's your head holding up?
Junko your boobies
always make me feel happy!
Stop it! That tickles!
Set these puppies free!
You awake?!
Yes, I'm awake. Stop shouting.
All right, Kosuna. Update me.
It's been one hour
since the first shot.
We've moved to a safer position
in this ancient missile silo.
Whoever that was took a
shot from a long way off.
I didn't hear it until
way after I saw it.
This guy's skilled.
The only damage he caused
though was to your head.
Oh, and I guess that
dent in the helmet, too.
Just an inch or two lower
and you would have been
in some serious trouble.
It looks like it destroyed the
enemy locator device inside.
That... dick!
What do you think our
next move should be?
Please, you have to help me.
Or we could just
leave her here to die.
If you want.
Grown-ups are talking.
Why don't you just shut up?
We're out of provisions
and ammunition.
We can't help.
Kosuna, I hear
what you're saying,
but we have to take this job.
What?
Have you lost it?
Thank you!
I do not approve of this.
Well, you don't have to...
It's my call, and I hate being
used by Junko as much as you do.
Believe me... But the thought...
The thought of her
marrying another man
fills me up with
maniacal rage!!!!
That's my boy, Kanta!
Step up to the plate!
Hold on.
Is there a condition?
Yes. After this
you agree to be mine.
No.
I swear, it's so pathetic to see
'the awesome Desert Punk
reduced to a needy pervert...
If you want me,
just be a man about it
and win me over with
your charm and dignity.
You suck.
You manage to pull that off
and I'll be your slave...
I'll do everything your sick
and twisted mind wants, me, to.
Are you serious?
Yes. And it won't
cost you anything.
You're offering up
free knocker rides?!
But you let me become
some other man's wife,
and none of this is ever
gonna happen for you...
Now, sign here.
And how!
I knew he'd crumble
under the pressure
of Junko's Utters. Moo.
He's alone.
Three hundred meters
to the north.
Three hundred?!
He got close fast.
Wait, Kosuna,
please don't tell me--
I already took care of it.
Which wasn't easy
while I was dragging
my unconscious Master
across the desert.
FINE!
He's wearing a
prototype desert suit.
What kind?
Don't know, but it has an
amazing tracking system.
Your usual bag of tricks
ain't gonna do it for us.
Is he really that good,
or are you just
blowing smoke up my--
He annihilated thirteen
fully loaded mercenaries
without blinking.
Yeah, he's good.
This is one of those
details you could
have informed me of before
I signed that contract.
Didn't she do this last time?
I'm sick of being shot at!
How can he squeeze off
such accurate shots
at night like that?
It's not him, it's the suit,
like I said before.
We're dead if we stay
stuck behind these rocks!
We're still waiting
for that plan of yours!
We're out of ammo and
we're in a crappy location.
We just have to run.
That's stupid!
Shut up!
Now line up single file!
Okay!
Not so fast.
Junko, you get in back.
Why me?
Dammit! I can't get a decent
shot with her in the way!
Guess they get to
live a little longer.
You're pissing me off, Junko.
What loser did you run
off and hire this time?!
At least it sounds like
the idiot fell for the trap.
Nope! He's still alive!
Man... If I'd have
known about his suit,
I would have set up
an explosive instead.
You set up a gas bomb?!
What's going on in
that tiny head of yours?!
That helmet's expensive...
I didn't want to blow it up.
You're so cheap
you were planning
on going back for the helmet?
Enough of the chatterboxing!
We gotta start running!
I'm going to get you... Junko!
Did we lose him?
Yeah, it looks like it.
But keep your eyes peeled.
We're safe inside
the Stone Forest...
A sniping attack,
here is impossible.
I just need a few minutes
to catch my breath.
I wouldn't get comfortable.
I've been trying to
outrun this guy for a week.
No matter what I did,
he always found me.
Maybe, but you weren't with
the demon of the desert then.
Start at the beginning.
Tell me the whole story.
You've heard of Ballsahurtin
Incorporated right?
Yeah, it's that desert suit
factory in the Northern Oasis.
That's where his prototype
suit was designed.
They excavated a
bunch of technology
from the Dark Ages and
reverse-engineered it illegally.
Contraband...! No wonder
he's giving us so much trouble.
He headed up the design
team for the prototype.
His name is Tech. Go figure.
Are you ever gonna get around
to why he's chasing you or not?
I wanted to know the things
Ballsahurtin had dug up
I tried to get close to them,
close enough to
know their secrets.
Junko, I want you
to run away with me.
What?
When I sell the
memory chip in this case
to that other company, they'll
pay millions for the data.
Back up... What are
you trying to tell me?
It's no secret how
I feel about you.
It's destiny. Come on, run away
with me and live the rich life!
Tech, you're not serious...
That chip is contraband...
It's not the kind of thing
that disappears into the night.
You're not making any sense.
Let me spell it out for you.
The only reasons
why you and I have
become so close is because
you're an expert in technology
and you work at Ballsahurtin.
You leave the company
and you're worthless to me.
Bitch--
Junko!
Don't you leave me...!
You walk out that
door and I'll find you!
I'll find you and make you mine!
You didn't have to
be such a bitch to him.
No wonder he's hunting you down.
Yeah, well, he irritated me.
Introducing Ballsahurtin
Incorporated's
newest prototype desert suit.
This new design is the ultimate
in lightweight desert luxury.
With a compact design and
reduced power consumption,
the suit comes complete with a
built-in air-conditioning system
and large-sized monitor,
in addition to the powerful
and highly accurate
enemy locator device.
Looks can be deceiving with
Ballsahurtin's new design,
considering that the suit
can be worn for almost
twice as long as any
other suit on the market,
your yen will go twice as far.
That's about the whole story.
If that prototype lasts
twice as long out here,
that's two times the jobs
and two times the money.
You think you can
get that suit off him?
And the deal stands
that if I rule
and kick his ass,
you'll be mine forever?
That's the deal.
But what do you say we wait
and see what actually plays out.
Have you two stopped to consider
how screwed we are here?!
I'm the only one with
an enemy locator device!
We're out of ammo!
We're down to just one battery!
And, oh yeah!
The temperature is about
to dip below zero
and we have no heaters!
Thanks for pointing all of
that out to us, Obvious Girl.
I have an insulated jump suit
and a few solar patches to
retain heat, so I'm good.
The real problem
here is that no matter
where we go or what we do,
this guy is gonna find us.
Junko...
Wow. You are a genius.
Ah... No, I'm not...
You're spending so much
money on me! I feel bad!
Forget about it!
It ain't nuthin'!
If your company
finds out about this,
you will be in trouble.
It just worries me so much.
Don't sweat it. It'll be
alright. I want you to take it.
You leave the company TECH...
and you're worthless to me.
He found us!
Yeah.
But how?
Where's he shooting from?
Shooting between these stone
pillars is nothing to him.
Not a chance!
No one could take those shots!
He's getting pretty close!
I'm telling you,
as long as he's wearing
that suit we've got
no place to hide!
Kosuna! Hit him with a flare!
You got it!
Smart move.
Looks like that may have
bought us some time--
Why don't you listen to me?!
I told you your old
BS tactics wouldn't work!
Shut up, I told
you--ohh, my coccyx.
You don't have your
night vision on, remember?!
You have to be more careful!
Well... this might be
the end of the line for us.
How can you say that?!
Don't give up, you pansy!
Face it! There's just no way
we can win against this guy!!
You're pathetic, Kanta...!
I thought you were going
to make me fall for you!
Be a man, and all that!
You're all washed up.
You're nothing but a
sad shadow of Desert Punk.
Say something else!
Open your mouth! I dare you!
I'm washed up?
Yeah, that's what I said.
You're supposed to rescue the
women, not act like one of them!
Uh, are you okay?
Punk? Hey, Punk?
I'm acting like
a woman! Washed up!
Ha ha ha! I'm awful, a loser!
A shadow of my
former self! Ha ha ha!
Well, it's about time.
Where did your
little saviors go?
They're hiding.
Probably setting their
sights on your head
and heart right about now.
No way.
There's no one within
two hundred meters.
During the day,
someone might have a shot.
But at night,
in the stone forest,
that range is
impossible for anyone else.
You never know,
unless you give it a shot.
You're wasting your time if you
think I'll get blinded twice.
I wouldn't be so
confident if I were you.
You wouldn't, huh?
Ohhh...
Yeah!
Impossible! My enemy locator
didn't pick up anything!
How did you get me?
Where were you hiding?
Take off the suit.
You do anything other
than that and you're dead.
Mud! You're covered in mud!
You did that to hide
your body heat, didn't you?
Then I heated the entire area
with that last flare we had.
After that, your
sensors couldn't see
the temperature variations.
And no matter how accurate
your enemy locator is,
it was still built
by human hands.
Wait, how did you
find mud in the desert?
There's not an oasis
out here for miles.
Cut it out!
Don't you dare
look at me right now!
Oh, it's warm like a tea bag.
You're sick.
Oh That is just nasty!
Yeah...
I can't believe
I was had by a guy
who rubbed pee-mud
all over himself!
Technology beaten by urine!
Ah... well played.
This suit was supposed
to make me unstoppable.
That's what you get for
screwing with technology.
A bullet and a big,
fat guilty conscience.
You might have learned
a lot today, Tech.
But the one lesson
I want you to leave here
with is the knowledge of what
an inexperienced
little boy you are.
Stop snotting in the
suit and take it off.
You have to tell me
one more thing! Please?
What is it?
How did you know
that I'd come in
so close for that last attack?
I wouldn't want
any man I didn't know
to be alone with Junko...
not for one solid
second in the day.
You got me more
figured out than I do.
Enough of the
slobbery loser routine!
Take the suit off already!
Tear gas--
Get back here!
I underestimated him. I failed.
I failed in
my promise to help her.
I broke the contract.
I'm an idiot. I gotta help...
Master!
Junko, here! With
superboobs and superdudes!
One of whom kidnapped me!
I didn't--
Uh huh!
She belongs to me!
Over poor little me?
I will kick!
And I will punch you!
Men are weird.
On the next Desert Punk,
'Too Close for Comfort"
Don't miss it or, uh...
things will happen!