Hey, you! Yeah, you!
The one on the couch!
Did you see the last episode?
Need a refresher?
That missile-chested poor excuse
of a whore Junko suckered
Master into another job.
And what do you know, it's a job
all about saving her stupid ass.
I told him we should
just walk away, but, no...
he doesn't listen.
Which is why, at this
moment, we are screwed.
Check out what happens.
Uh, Junko?!
ESPERA! QUE PASO AQUI?!
Come on...! Dinnertime, kids!
Don't tell me you
squeezed out another one?
That makes number six!
Daddy's gonna have to work much
harder now to feed all of us.
Don't you know it!
Es muy tarde! Porqué
estoy soñando en español.
What the hell?
Why do I dream in Spanish?
We over slept...!
Look how high the moon is!
It's late...!
Oh, no... jerk... moron...
Yeah... I hate
sleeping on rocks.
It always makes my butt hurt.
You're, uh... In my...
Oh, Master...
What are you doing up?
Hello...! You have
no business sleeping
in the same bag
with a grown man...
What's wrong with your brain...?
Although I do understand
how you can be drawn in
by my striking good looks
and giant muscles.
Check out that ego...
I was only sleeping next
to you to keep us warm...
We could have frozen
to death out here
if I hadn't done it, tool.
Sick!
He stinks like pee!
We could have used
my suit's heater,
and drained our only battery...
But we'd be nailed to the wall
without the enemy locator
device... You get it?!
That's why I warmed your
nasty body up with mine.
So are we gonna go after that
skank or let her get married?
Let's see what my
other head is thinking.
Ooo, let's go save her!
Stop dragging your heels!
This is an emergency situation!
Emergency?
It's been hours since they left,
and we stopped for a nap.
Shut up.
I bet they're doing it.
Cork it!
No slimeball smart-guy is
gonna lay a hand on Junko!
I'll show him what's what!
Yeah, he'll be hurting!
If I'm not mistaken, lover boy,
you've had plenty
of opportunities
with Junko and
you have yet to score.
Are you limp or something?
A man's heart is a deep ocean.
There's no way there'd be time.
He'd have to haul
her off, marry her,
and then somehow
manage to convince her...
Master? Master, look at this!
What?! What is it?!
Look at what?!
Don't mean to be paranoid,
but that's three of those
prototype suits, right?
Ballsahurtin Incorporated
must have sent
out a team to find Tech.
Do you think they
know we're here?
With those suits on, they might.
But they don't act like it.
Maybe they're just
keeping a low profile
until they can
pounce on their target.
We can't fight four
guys in those outfits.
They'd shred us
into minced meat.
They're walking away.
What are we gonna do?
We're almost out of ammo...
There's no choice.
We have to deal with them.
The trick is
finding the leverage.
Kosuna, what's
our exact location?
If I'm right,
which I usually am,
there's an abandoned
mine nearby.
Uh, yeah, lemme see.
It's about an hours
walk to the west.
Excellent. Time for a pit stop.
You still can't figure out how
to repair that busted com?
How could you tell?
Just a lucky guess.
You think taking that sucker
apart here is a good idea?
That hardware's delicate.
I know what I'm doing...
Fix two or three things...
I'm good.
Do you have any idea
how screwed you are?
Yeah... I thought everything
was going to be smooth...
I can't blame any of this on
my lack of skills or the suit.
It's that Desert Punk of yours.
I don't think I've ever seen
eyes like that on a person.
But the first ones you
hired out to rescue you,
those guys gave me
a bit of a scare.
Thanks to my suit, I didn't
have too much of a problem.
The second chump you hired out
was fairly well known,
if I'm not mistaken.
The third one was a
collector, I think.
The fourth was an inquirer.
And they all failed.
Don't count your chickens yet.
I'm still alive.
I wonder... How many you killed.
What the-- What's that?!
That's Desert Punk!
No way!
I knew it... I'm saved.
Help me Punk...! I'm in here...!
You gotta hurry...!
He's already got me naked!
Tech?! Who's with you in there?
I see you. And your friend.
I guess you and your
little girlfriend made up.
You have no idea
the shit you're in.
Tech... Who are they...?
Tell me.
Ballsahurtin Incorporated
sent them to find me.
And bring me back. Oh no!
That's cheap for
such good stuff.
Are you serious?
The suits they have are models
D, E, and F of the prototype.
I only have Type C.
And if I know those voices,
it's the same crazy mercenaries
hired to test the suits.
Come on, Tech, my man.
I'm gonna be nice
and give you ten minutes
to scuttle your ass out here.
Yeah. Do that,
and we won't bury you alive.
I'd take that deal
if I were you.
You gotta give up...
They said they'd let
you live if you just go!
He's on his way...!
That's right...! He surrenders!
If we walk out of here,
they'll kill us...
You have no idea
who you're dealing with.
I'll run a distraction...
When I do, you get outta here.
Tech, you can't stay.
It's not like that.
I'm not giving up
my life for yours.
I have things I want to do.
See the world, Ventriloquism .
I'm gonna make it out of this!
I refuse to die today!
I GOT DREAMS.
His time's up. What's our move?
We're dealing with a death wish.
We'll deliver. Kill him.
There you are, C-Type!
How can he hit us
from so far away?!
It's the suit. C-Type suits have
more accurate distance counters.
They ditched it with our suits
to make room
for the shit locker.
Would you two
stop chatting it up?!
I can't focus on my aim when
you two pop off like ninnies!
He's on the move!
What's he doing leaving
the woman behind?
How should I know?!
And don't kill him.
I've got about a hundred
questions for the thief.
Okay, I'll just
take out his legs.
Corner him in the ravine!
You got it!
Akagi! Go after the girl!
He's trying to give
her time to escape!
Can do!
And watch your ass.
That chick's no
featherweight. She's lethal.
Trust me. I'll be fine.
You know...
You're not a bad fighter
for an engineer,
but I gotta ask,
is the broad worth all this.
Uh, yes. She absolutely is.
Sounds like she's
my kind of girl.
Busted!
It's Desert Punk!
He's flying!
I thought you
were alone out here!
To hell with being outnumbered!
He's running away.
A coward's always a coward.
He's got that prototype on and
he's still scared.
But you know what I always say.
There's a time to stay, and a
time to run like a little bitch.
Here.
I assume you'll feel more
comfortable with that one.
Me? I'm taking this
bad boy right here.
What is this guy thinking...?
It's even loaded.
This must be...
Those guys are after you,
and you got Junko ...
Which puts us on
the same side...
You and I can settle
our differences as soon as
we send those blowhards packing.
If you don't like
the sound of that...
Then shoot me in the back
and see how far you
get fighting alone.
I'm in.
All my life is spent
with one jerk or another
chasing down my ass!
She's got a nice ass.
It'll make a good target.
I know that...
That's Desert Punk's mark.
I have no idea what I'm doing!
Left here!
A dead end!
You gotta be jerking my chain!
End of the line for you, baby.
But, damn, chasing
you sure looked good.
Don't shoot!
Please, don't kill me.
I'll do anything you want!
That true? Anything?
Of course...!
Whatever you want...
We could get busy here or...
If you got a sleeping bag,
it'd be warmer.
You mean the sex.
Yeah... the sex.
Tempting.
It can be more than that.
I can do all kinds of things.
Ya know , whatever your into.
Too bad I've got an
issues with slutty chicks.
I can't believe I missed!
Where the hell did
you come from?!
Come on out! I just wanna talk!
This is it! The end!
The big sleep!
I said I wanted to talk to you!
Talk to this.
Nice
Enough!, you sound like a pig!
Master!!
The grenade didn't do it.
Figures.
I'd live forever if
I had one of those suits
and you shooting at me.
If I hadn't lured that
dingbat down this dead end,
I would have never
gotten close enough
for any kind of shot on him.
And just who are you
calling dingbat, huh?
You.
Enough! You can't
just use me as a decoy
just to lure that
doofus Tech out of hiding!
Tech, what are you--high?!
We're all gonna
help each other out
until those Ballsahurtin
farts are done with.
Huh?
I can't afford to act
like an idiot any more.
Has the world gone crazy?
Two hours till sun-up.
We just have to
watch each others backs
for a little while longer.
Do you have a plan
or are we coasting?
I always have a plan.
And a backup.
And another backup.
Come on... It's me.
Maybe we can take cover
behind his huge ego.
We use the daylight.
How do we do that?
I make it two men with Tech.
That's not including the girl.
They ambushed us
once they can do it again.
They're not leaving
this desert alive.
Let's show them what
these suits can really do.
Give Tech the feel of what
it's like to be a hunted dog.
I'll fire off as
many rounds as I want!
What do you know desk jockey?!
That's not what it
says in the manual.
It says--
Yes! Yeah!
You were a damn
good engineer, Tech.
Why'd you have to do it?
Stay behind your desk,
do your job.
But no. You had to come out here
and ruin a
perfectly good career.
Don't worry.
They're just showing off
their suits like spoiled kids.
Those spoiled kids are
close to shooting my face off!
We can't get outta here!
Five...
Four...
Three...
Two...
One...
Master, they're here!!
The cavalry!
Right on!
That did it!
Are... Are those tanks?
Those are government tanks.
And you win a prize!
You son of a ...
I keep my word...
I told you we'd
settle our differences
when those guys are done for...
And from the looks of it,
they're out of escape routes.
TANKS! I JUST
FILLED THAT LOCKER!
Please, do not try to escape.
We have you surrounded.
Please, put down your weapons.
We have your surrounded.
Please, give up, already.
We have you surrounded.
No talking tank's gonna
tell me what to do!
Don't tell me you actually
called in the government.
Oh, I did...
Not too far from here
is an abandoned mine.
It used to be a
government place,
and there's still
a top-secret hard-line
to those losers
hooked up inside.
A hard-line?
Yeah, a phone.
Only the top government
jerks and their close,
personal pals know
about this place.
I knew it...!
You're a government rat!
A rat. I don't think so.
I just know the right people...
And today it happened
to save your ass.
Think about it. Who's the enemy?
The guys who work
for Ballsahurtin?
No. We kill these
three or four guys,
and they'll send eight
to kill us next time.
Then twelve.
But if we take down
the entire corporation...
Problem gone... Then we win.
What...? Ballsahurtin's gone?
Well played again,
Man Im a loser!
Words to live by. I always win.
I don't care what it takes,
I will have my victory!
I lost everything...
Thanks to you and all
the dirt you stirred up,
we were able to uncover all
of the Ballsahurtin
Incorporated secrets.
Now that the
North Government has
all of the evidence it needs,
we will shut down Ballsahurtin
for unethical scientific work
and treasonous activities.
Those at the top
will be executed.
The companies'
one thousand employees
and their families will all
be banished to the desert.
And... it's all my fault.
They did it...!
They threatened to fire me...!
I said I was gonna
tell what I knew!
What a loser...
I don't know any guy
who doesn't act like that...
Always thinking with that
slower second brain of theirs.
You bitch.
This is all your fault.
Our old merc, Junko.
I hear you've had
some business up north...
The illegal kind of business.
What do you mean?
Don't worry. I'm not
going to arrest you.
I just need your cooperation.
A helpful hand, if you will.
Nothing that's going
to put you in harm's way.
Whoa, no way! Hold up!
What the... There you are!
Who are you?
Hi...
This piece of tail owes me
a buncha cash as
you can see here...
We have a binding contract.
If you take her away,
I can't get paid.
I got a government
seal and everything.
Prick...! What do you think--
Master!
Of course, nothing
happened here today...
There were no witnesses to
any of this... Are we clear?
Help, me!
Let go...!
Get your mitts off...!
You're making me-Master!
Are you okay?
I need some help! Somebody!
He needs a doctor! Help, please!
Master!
Everyone just left.
All of that, and we're
left with a big goose egg.
Man, I'm hungry.
But it serves that
dumb bimbo right!
She deserves whatever
those soldiers are going
to put through her.
Get it?
Pretty good one, huh? Huh?
Let's go.
Okay.
On the walk home,
he didn't say a word to me.
Of course, with
that swollen mouth,
it probably didn't
feel too good to talk.
I don't think the banged up ego
helped the situation
much, either.
I never thought a
signed contract could be
torn up like that.
It makes me think...
Is everything we do as
fragile as a piece of paper?
I hope not.
I am the demon of the desert--
I'm sick of how you keep pulling
your punches on these outros.
You gotta pump up.
You're just phoning this in.
Next Time,
'Scratching the Surface."
Uh, better. But not
really. Anyway--
Miss the next episode
and be sorry.
That's my line.