Hey, everybody!
As you know, I'm only fourteen
but I'm working everyday
to be Kanto Desert's
number one power babe!
I've got crazy skills!
Whenever there's trouble,
I'll go into super-fly
mercenary mode!
I'll blow everyone away and
I won't take any prisoners!
Ta-da!
What the hell is this?!
What'dya mean boss?
It's a freakin' pit you moron!
Hold up! This place is
rigged so watch your step!
Now that I think about it...
What am I doing here?
Am I just wasting my time being
Desert Punk's number two?
I want to become a
powerful mega-babe,
but it sure doesn't seem like
I'm getting any
closer to my goal.
Sometimes, I just don't know...
They're on the move!
Heading south fast...!
Hello...! Kosuna,
do you copy? Come in!
Oh... what?!
Don't just sit there!
Go gather up those balloons
right now, you copy?
Roger that!
Who is this creep?
He's freakin nuts!
Cool your jets!
I think we lost him...
Hey bitches...
Hey where'd he go?!
How in the hell did he do that?!
Who cares let's get outta here!
Help!
Hey, he took his pants!
Why'd he take his pants?
What did he do to you?
It's like high school
all over again!!
I'm getting outta here...
I don't want him
taking my pants off.
Wait...! Wait for me!
Why did I get up this morning?!
Yay, there's another one.
Only two balloons to go.
Who am I kidding?
This is a total
waste of my time.
I'll never get to be a
power babe doing this crap.
I need to strut my stuff and
show this desert who's boss.
You're mine now you damn fool!
Oh no, how could
I have been so stupid?!
Who knew this guy had
a knack for tricks.
Say your prayers Desert Punk...
This will be your final
resting place ... Fire!
Hurry! We, gotta
find that sniper now!
Whoa, that was close!
Thanks for saving me,
whoever you are!
It was me! Kanto's
number one power babe!
If you want to live
another day you'll take
my advice and get out
of my desert! Pronto!
Kosuna...?
I can't believe it,
you're Kanto's most beautiful
and dangerous power-babe ever,
can I get your autograph!
We love you Kosuna!
You're the greatest
power-babe ever!
We're not worthy!
You saved my life Kosuna,
I owe you one big time.
It's obvious you don't need me
telling you what to do anymore.
You truly are the
greatest mercenary ever.
She's almost
better than pudding.
Hip, hip, hooray!
Maybe someday...
For now I guess I'm stuck here
dealing with these jerk-weeds.
Who you calling a jerk-weed?!
Balloons and a shovel...
So, you're the one setting
all these freakin' traps...!
It's pay back time!
I'm gonna beat you till
the white meat shows!!
Bullet proof...! Oh crud!
That all you got?!
Help!
Damn!
Look at him--dumb
meathead should have
headed back to camp and spared
himself some busted chops.
Master...
You know you set
yourself up for that one?
I know the guy jumped you
but he wasn't even armed
and he still stuck it to you.
Now, what would you have
done if I hadn't come along?
I don't know...
You're really going to
have to pick up your game
if you want to survive
out here, young lady.
I'm sorry, sir.
The fact is you should be able
to handle a job like
this on your own.
I've got better things to do.
There's no way I can
protect you all the time.
Okay...
You're always off in la-la land
when you should be
doing your job.
That's your problem,
your delusions of grandeur.
Get over it!
Yeah, guess you're right.
You're turning out to be
more pain than you're worth.
I paid too much for
an AK for it to jam up!
You, think it's busted?
It's the sand that
clogs up these fully-autos.
Maybe the old man can fix it.
Do you think I'm dumb?!
Don't try and scam me
you damn scumbag...
I know you broke
the gun yourself.
But, I didn't break it...
Shut up...! If it's
giving you so much trouble
maybe you should
just carry a knife...
Get the hell out of my shop...!
Before I put a
few rounds in you!
Slow down!
Hey--
Business as usual, huh Igara.
Look, my favorite shit-head...
I see you're still alive.
Yeah, thanks to you, pal.
What can I do you for?
We need to fix the brat here
up with a new piece. Pronto.
How do you do sir?
My name's Kosuna, I work for
Desert Punk--I'm his apprentice.
It's an honor...
We were on a job
a day or two ago
and some happy jack gave
her a run for her money.
She claims her gun
wasn't powerful enough
to stop the guy--I don't know.
I shot the guy like
five times in the chest
and he still didn't go down!
If I had blasted him
with a more powerful gun,
he would have been toast.
It's not about getting your
self into a gunfight out there.
Anybody can do
something as easy as that.
The trick to it all
is not being spotted.
I know and I agree
but still if only I had--
I just have to...
I have to be able to get
myself out of my own mess...
You understand.
Ohh...
You know... you've been doing
an awful lot of your own
thinking here lately...
A real mercenary
doesn't need to think!
What do you know?!
All you care about are giant
cans and a nice piece of ass!
Follow me...
I've got just the thing.
How 'bout this one?
No good?
You know what I really want?
A 308 caliber assault rifle
and a big 357 magnum pistol.
Pipe down...
That stuff ain't cheap.
I know you think I'm
just a stupid little kid...
but I know what
I'm talking about.
Why can't you just trust
me for once and hook me up?
I need power...
Something that will knock 'em
to the freakin' ground
when I shoot it.
Okay... You have to
show me something first...
You have to prove to me...
that you're tough enough to
carry a bigger weapon got it?
Okay, fine.
I'll shoot any gun you've got!
Very well then...
Great! How about the 223?
Or do you want me to take
a stab at the 308 first?
Go dig some holes for awhile?
The shovels are over there.
I'll get right on it.
I came to get a gun...
Why am I digging stupid holes?
Are you sure?
Don't you think you
should use the biggest one?
I see what he's up to.
This shovel's heavy...
My shoulder
muscles are burning...!
I know what he's trying to do...
Trying to teach me
to see my own limitations...
So, I'll choose a gun
that's best for my size.
You're such a cutie pie!
Screw that old fart!
I'll show him.
He thinks I'll
give up, but I won't.
He wants to teach me a
lesson? I'll give him one.
I need a gun with
power--I want that 308.
I need a weapon that
will rock the house!
So, sounds like those amateurs
are still at it, aren't they?
Yeah, up north in Skeleton City.
That was Kaplan
and Tanshon right...?
They're so worthless, you
shouldn't even waste your time.
I know, but I couldn't resist.
The job came down from
Mugenya and I had to take it.
It'll be over as soon as
the bodyguard gets out
of the hospital though.
Moron caught appendicitis.
Is that what I think it is?
You're good kid...
Most wouldn't notice.
So, it is then!
That's right...
At first glance it looks
like any other M2 clone...
but this one is an original.
I'm sure you already
know that the guns
we have here in the Kanto
are all replicas of old guns
discovered from the Dark Ages.
The originals excavated
from Skeleton City
have long since been confiscated
by the Oasis government
and hidden away.
Every now and then, after
they've taken them apart,
studied them and drawn up plans
to manufacture the replicas,
you'll see 'em out
on the black market.
I guess even the government
has people who can't be trusted.
They say, somewhere
out in the desert,
somewhere very secret,
deep beneath the sand,
there are government storerooms
filled with original weaponry.
Course it's very well guarded.
I hear it's a treasure
trove of all kinds of stuff.
Yeah, I've never seen it,
only heard rumors about it,
but I hear there's stuff there
they can't even figure out.
The technology
was just ahead of us.
Things from the
Super Technology era
that basically brought
about the Dark Ages.
So, what do you think of it?
It's totally different
than the knockoffs
being sold around town.
Don't you think?
Sounds good, huh?
The steel is a
vastly superior quality
than anything you
see these days.
From the materials to the
engineering to the accuracy...
everything's first class.
So, who does this
beauty belong to...?
Must be a millionaire or someone
with really good
government connections...
It had to have cost a fortune.
That looks familiar.
I've seen that retarded
chicken scratch before.
Desert Punk slacking off.
Imagine that.
Why do you always
have to be so annoying?
I don't think it's just
me that annoys you.
I think it's the fact
that the big, bad Desert Punk
got played by that run around.
What's her name? Junko?
Am I right Desert Puke?
And what about you,
Stain Spider?
All that work with
the Inumeiwa rock?
That's working out pretty
good for you isn't it?
Anyway, how's that
gun I asked you
to have a look at coming along?
I've been pretty busy lately so,
I guess I could really
use a couple more days.
That's okay...
I want it in tip-top
shape so you take
whatever time you need,
just not too long, all right?
Hey, loser!
What?
You seem to be doing pretty well
for yourself these
days lame Spider...
Are collections
that profitable now?
I'm not collecting anymore.
Huh?
Igara, I will be back.
Good, you can pay for the door
when you pick up your gun.
Of course. I intend to.
Wait?!
Take my advice punk--
You won't find money stuffed
in a poor man's mattress.
You know where you
find real treasure?
Where?
On the battlefield.
I don't know how he's doing it,
but that guy does seem to
have a good source of cash-flow.
What a duncebucket ...
I can't believe
that guy's giving up
on his collections business.
What's he thinking?
You're one to talk...
What are you gonna do,
be a damn mercenary
for the rest of your life?
I think you may be giving me
a little more credit
than I deserve.
You're probably right.
Well, let's get goin'.
I'm sure she's had enough.
Wake up...! You're not dead yet!
Wa-water...
Here you go.
Thank, you!
Slow down...
You don't wanna cramp up.
What?
Look here--
Here it is... the one
you wanted, right?
The 308 caliber
fully automatic, FN line...
It's a bit heavier
than the G3 model
but in the desert there's
nothing more deadly.
This sucker's heavy.
I can do it!
100 meters on her first try.
This is... unbelievable.
Amazing...
It's almost too much for me.
My shoulder's killing me.
It's way too heavy
and the recoil is pounding
the crap out of me.
I don't know that I could
handle this for a
long time in a battle.
The AK recoils even worse...
It's too light for
it's power... So, then...
Which one do you want
to try out next...?..
If you like, I've got an M4
or a 64 you could test out...
I guess it was too
much for me after all...
If I were to walk through
the hot desert with this...
plus the weight of extra ammo...
I'd be exhausted.
I couldn't do anything else
and that wouldn't
be good for anybody.
A gun is a tool...
And all tools can either
help you or hurt you...
just because you
have a powerful tool
doesn't make you
a powerful person...
Just look at him.
You mean me?
I've been around for 55 years
and I've never known such
a low despicable person.
I can hear you!
He's a cheap, cowardly,
spiteful bottom feeder,
and for some reason
he seems to think he's
better than everyone else.
Okay now wait, you don't
really mean that do you?
However...
However, what really
makes me so angry
at this piece of crap punk
is the way he runs around
the Great Kanto Desert
like a renegade...
with nothing more
than a beat up,
hand-me-down scatter-gun
he got from his dad.
He's had a
308 caliber rifle, rocket
and grenade launchers, even
a hovercraft over the years.
But he still wanders around
with that old shotgun
and nothing more.
Living carefree from day to
day like nothing else mattered.
It just goes to show
you just how unscrupulous
and self-centered he's
been all these years...
no more than a filthy coward.
I'm just trying to make a
living Igara, jeez back off.
See what a sniveling fool he is?
Yes... And, I think
he's very tough.
So, you think he's
a tough guy, huh?
That's when I realized
what I really wanted
and it wasn't a big monster gun.
I finally got a glimpse
of who I wanted to be,
what I wanted to be.
Tough and smart...
just like him. Wow...
That's sweet!
You like it?
It's perfect, just right for me.
Hold on, let me
adjust it a little more.
Hey great!
Yo!
Yes, Master?
That little 9mm
machine gun has less power
but it's still going to take
some time to get used to it.
Oh, yeah... I know...
I'll figure it out quickly.
Okay, we'll see about that.
Just great! This must
mean that the old man
thinks she's got what it takes
to handle a weapon like that.
She's gonna get a
big head over this.
I just want to be very
clear about something.
A hot woman with a
nice set of milk missiles
doesn't need a big gun
to get ahead in the world.
Let's get out of here!
Where the hell did he go?!
Run, just run!
It's a trap!
Another pit!
Watch out!
Missed him.
He disappeared!
Kosuna, I've taken care of
the enemy in Sector 11 South...
Get ready in Sector 8 North,
I'll be sending them that way!
Look sharp, okay?
Got it!
The sand is hot!
It's burning things!
Man I haven't shot
a single bullet all day...
Crap! I gotta get
to work in Sector 8!
I need to stop daydreaming
and focus on the task at hand.
Even if I'm only
digging holes all day,
I'm still in training to be
Kanto's number one power-babe.
I know what I want to be
and I have to
work at it everyday.
But I have to remember
what Igara taught me:
a wise person
understands his limitations
and doesn't try and soar
farther than his wings
will take him... or her.
Kosuna here, the soon to be mega
power-babe of the Kanto Desert!
Don't listen to her
she's still an amateur.
Everyone's gonna make out
on the next episode,
One-eared Dogs and Idiot Frogs.
No! The real next episode
is "The Girl Next Door"!
Hey did notice the
new theme song?