So what do you
two guys want from me?
Where's that little
wart of yours?
You know, your apprentice?
I figured that she'd be
stuck to you as usual.
This isn't a job, Akio.
It's a meeting, so the
girl's on her own today.
And what about Haru?
I didn't think any one of
you guys could take a leak
without the other
two spotting for him.
What?!
Haru's got a date today.
Well... where did he
meet this mystery man?
Watch your mouth!
I'm really impressed
with you Punk.
You actually showed up unarmed
just like we agreed we would.
I didn't need to
bring my gun. I trust you.
That's still one hell of a
leap of faith, if you ask me...
I thought you stayed
armed no matter what.
But you're my friends... right?
Listen... If you see
any of them make a move
for me or pull a gun,
you start shooting.
What a bunch of
crappy childhood friends.
He can't even trust
them to not kill him.
That's Haru.
I'm glad my
friends don't hate me...
Course I don't really
have any friends.
We figured that you owe us.
How's that?
We saved your life, Punk.
You got me there.
But if you've come
asking for money,
I am way short
on funds these days.
No, we need you in on a job.
A job? No kidding.
Why didn't you just hire me
through Mugenya
like anyone else?
Cause it's not ours...
Natsuko asked us to
find you and hire you for it.
What...?
Natsuko's coming back home?
He's moving in for the kill!
Here we go!
Idiot.
And... That's why
I'm always armed.
You broke your word!
So did you.
Now, fill me in on Natsuko.
When's she getting here?
Soon.
Hold on... Isn't she working
at that Oasis Government office?
Yeah.
So this is a freaking
government job?
Farts if I know.
Why don't you ask her.
Fine... But I don't
do government jobs.
Speaking of...
Fuyo! Akio! Haru!
I missed you guys,
how've you been.
Whoa! You've exploded
into quite a woman!
Kanta?
And your boobs are way bigger
than the mosquito
bites they used to be!
You haven't changed!
So... Fill me in
on this job chicky.
Well, it's at the
government's request...
and it's worth a lot of cash.
Yes...! One government job
and you're pretty
much set, for life!
Sweet!
For real...? Great!
This is straight panties.
Not to mention security
and a thick wallet look
real good to the chicks...
Damn, I haven't
been laid in years.
Someone out there
somewhere is in trouble today
Waiting somewhere for
someone to show them the way
That's the time that you and me
will show them
that we are hardcore
Help them out
or kick their butts,
whatever we are hired for--
The West Oasis
Mercenary Association,
We are your heroes,
We are your salvation!
This thing is a
hunk of steely cool.
It belongs to the government.
Of course it's cool.
It looks like it
could do some damage.
Just be sure you're
not in the way
when it does,
got that butt-munchkin?
Whatever. I'm just
thrilled that a chic
is the captain of
this whole thing.
Natsuko is my kind of woman.
Nothing like a crap in the
morning to clean the ol' pipes.
Tube connected and locked!
Roger that! Open the valve!
Oh, that is just disgusting.
You hear that noise?
I can't believe this crap.
I guess I just
expected a little more.
But this is the government.
What's the matter, master?
I thought the
government might give us
something cool to do.
You know with a
little responsibility.
But it turns out
they're just using us
to haul last night's lasagna.
Don't think of it like that.
Didn't Natsuko say this
job was extremely important
to food distribution in
the West Oasis district?
Something like that.
Still, the only crap
I like smelling is my own.
Stop! You're not allowed
to use those toilets!
But I really have
to go! I'm cramping!
Those toilets are for Oasis
government officials only!
Get your damn hand off me!
Captain it's you!
Oh, crap.
We need the fertilizer
to grow our food.
That's how we stay alive...
Without recycling
the settler's shit,
we wouldn't have
it for the crops.
Then we'd have no food.
Without him we don't eat,
so you let the man
crap wherever he wants.
Are we clear?
I'm sorry captain!
I'll do whatever you say!
Just don't dock my pay!
I'm sorry!
It's okay, old timer...
You can take care of business
in any toilet you want.
Oh, holy mahogany,
here it comes!
That kicked ass!
Did you see how
she brought that lackey
to his knees without
even raising a fist?!
Yeah well she used to
be a crybaby... shut up.
We don't have time to
jerk around. Let's go.
I don't know about you,
but it sounds like she
kicked that crybaby problem.
She's joking.
Natsuko always
loved a good laugh.
She used to always joke
like that when we were kids.
Really. I swear... I know.
You're totally convincing.
We have to hit the next
watering hole by sundown.
Let's get this rig on the move.
Yes, ma'am.
Our sister's ordering
those soldiers around.
She totally got that from me!
That's her job now, doof.
She's the captain.
Don't you pay attention?
Here's to our kid sister!
From the bottom of the world
to the top of the military!
Today, she commands
both--the Oasis soldiers
and the Machinegun Brothers!
Ah, it's good times for all.
Uh, what did you say?
We couldn't hear you.
I said it looked like you
were having a good time.
Hell yes!
We don't get picked up
for the good jobs
like this one too often.
Yeah... I didn't figure anyone
with a brain would have
taken this stinkin' job...
unless of course they
were somehow related
to Captain Panties up there.
What did you say...?
And you better think
before you answer!
I'm saying that
we're hauling shit...!
No one's gonna try to steal it!
You think this assignment is
given to a captain worth a piss?
Or do you think
they'd dump it off
on the lowest bitch
on the totem pole?
So if you dudes work
for the lowest bitch,
I guess that would just make
you the diseased horse flies
buzzing around the shit!
Keep laughing!
Ass!
Dance monkeys!
Uh, hey... sis
We were just, uh, introducing
ourselves to the soldiers.
You know, thought it'd be best
to know each
others names and all.
We get to our posts right away.
The load is
completely on deck...
We'll be departing at once.
Ma'am.
You--
That's for
embarrassing our sister!
Sorry, bro...
I just... I lost it.
Well, find it and stick it back
in that empty canyon of a head.
Akio, you dumb--
Enough. We got work to do.
Any bodyguards?
Besides the soldiers, there
were about five mercenaries.
Then they haven't
caught wind of us yet.
If they had, they'd have way
more than five mercs
and some soldiers.
It may have
looked like only five.
But Desert Punk
is among those men.
Not the demon of the desert?!
The very same. And if you
think he's just one man...
You haven't seen anything yet.
Master, what did
that soldier mean
when he said that
no one would bother
to steal anything off this rig?
Shit is shit.
But it's valuable for us.
The trick is that you
need tons of the stuff,
much more than
this truck can haul,'
if's it to be useful
or worth anything.
So no matter what you
gotta go through to get it,
you'd have a hard
time getting paid?
Someone wanting to
steal one truck of shit
would have to be
hardcore badass enough
to steal hundreds.
So the rigs cross the desert one
at a time to cut down on theft.
What the crap was that?
Road's blocked.
Those rocks out there
are blocking the road.
I'm aware. Why don't you
guys go check that out?
Aye-Aye Cap'n!
Keep your eyes peeled!
What do you think it is?
A trap set up by
the sand pirates
to kilo us all... dumbass
Well? Can we make it through?
Not without a load of dynamite.
I doubt we can go around either.
The sand would get too deep
and the tires would sink.
We'd have no traction.
Hey...! What?
The radio's jammed.
I can't raise anyone.
We're under attack!!
A trap...
Man, that stings! I guess
that means I'm still alive.
No! Fuyo!
Get up, man! What do we do?!
His ribs are broken.
I hope he's not
bleeding internally.
We gotta get back to the rig!
I can guarantee
you that won't happen.
Miss me?
I couldn't miss the stink.
You know you should
really consider wiping.
You haven't changed either.
Predictable as ever.
I believe you and
I have somewhat
of a score to settle,
Desert Punk.
What do you say we
pick up where we left off?
You can have everything!
Please, just don't
search my cavity!
I know what you
guys do to people!
Man, Haru is such a vag.
To think that Rain Spider,
the number one collector
in the South Oasis...
Would stoop to the level
of the common thief?!
I wouldn't have to
if it wasn't for you!
What?
You mean that you
screw up out in the field
and you blame it
all on me? Grow up.
Enough.
You're dead before the
smoke clears on this scene.
Look at it this way--You
die, you become a legend.
He's had those weapons
stored up for this operation.
That means he's well prepared.
Which pretty much means
I'm dead in the water.
I catch your drift.
You're here to take ownership
of the West Oasis rig.
Oh, looks like he's
trying to set these guys up.
Could be funny.
You geniuses have any
idea what this rig is hauling?
I hope you know
what you're getting into.
Is it not hauling shit?
You mean you
came after this load
knowing full well
what it contained?
Of course, I did.
Uh... Oh...kay...
It was a bold move.
I give you that.
Yes. I know.
What's going on?
You two can get kinda weird--
He's frozen
completely stone solid.
I've never seen him
look so tense before.
Oh no.
If we were attacked
by people who knew
about the shit, then they'd
have to be hardcore badasses,
just like master said.
Oh, we're screwed.
Damn! They've got
gunners on board!
Pick up your feet Haru!
I'm trying!
Jump, Kosuna!
They have a decisive commander.
I admire that about them.
Too bad Desert Punk got away.
No worries. The operation
went according to plan.
Natsuko--
I mean, Captain...
Can we stop at a
town with a doctor?
Fuyo looks like he's
doing worse by the second.
He could be a mess inside
and we'd never know
without a doctor's help.
Sorry, but we can't...
We're going straight
to West Oasis...
Wait--
Our first priority
is to get the truck
and its contents
safely to the Oasis.
But our brother?!
You should listen to
your Captain, Akio...
If we lose this truck we lose
everything, including our rep.
The best thing to do
in this situation
is keep moving so
they can't hit you.
But...
How's my box?
The signal is fried, even though
it's not that strong
a jamming frequency.
But the area it covers is huge.
I didn't think
they could do that.
Oh, no.
We're all gonna die!
They're crawling
all over the rig!
Master, what are we gonna do?!
Stay on the ground!
Akio!
Clean these goons
off the other side!
Cool!
Shut this door and
lock it behind you.
But--
That's an order!
If they take control
of this rig, we are dead!
Yes, ma'am!
I'll flank them
to the other side.
You just keep them pinned down.
Don't order me around!
Just move your ass!
All the big guns are useless
with these guys
all over the rig.
We'd just blow ourselves away.
Gotta find something else.
What do we do?
We can't even see 'em!
Either of you notice
your captain's, gone?
What?!
Where is she?!
That coward!
She's locked herself
in the control room!
Captain my ass!
Freakin' desert woman.
You idiot!
You'll get yourself killed!
That's why all of the
shots are over our heads.
The morons can't even see us!
They're shooting blind!
Time for Kosuna
to save the day...
Out here it doesn't matter
if you're a woman
or from the desert.
When you're good, you're good.
What the crap?
This wasn't here before...
Knock knock.
Who's there?
Cut it out!
That was close.
I knew it. I just knew it.
She's the baddest chic
in the Kanto Desert!
I hope it hurts when
you hit the ground!
Goon H, does coffee
make you poo?
You know something
Goon G... It does.
I really hurt...
The back of the rig is secure.
How's the front?
Taken care of, ma'am.
Double check and
make sure we're clear.
Aye Aye, Captain.
What you did
was really stupid...
You could've been killed.
Don't do it again.
Oh, no... I won't...
That being said...
I have to say thank you...
Without your distraction,
I would have never
have had the chance to jump down
and take those fellas out...
You really saved the day.
Thanks! I'm happy
that I could help!
So... What was that about?
That's right...! Natsuko
just thanked me for my help.
What for?
I distracted them--
Then she jumped in
and put the smack down!
Huh?
Oh, yeah... It was...
Like Stryker...!
Remember all of his cool Kenpo?
She moved just like he did!
He okay?
I think so. He's sleeping now...
That soldier over there
gave him a shot of morphine.
Yeah...
This sucks.
It'll be morning before we
can get these parts repaired.
It'd be easier if we
could radio for help.
Yes it would Captain obvious.
I just wish we knew
where they were sending
their jamming signal from.
Did you hear what
that kid was saying?
About the captain using Kenpo?
Yeah, which means she underwent
special ops training...
But I don't know who'd let
a desert person into that.
I'm starting to think
this mission isn't
about hauling shit.
It might be a cover.
Why not...?
With a Kenpo captain and a
handful of mercs on our side,'
I'd believe anything
at this point.
What's the deal Punk?
You're never this serious
around the ol' campfire.
It's our happy fun mantime.
There's a lot about
this mission I don't like...
That includes our
enemy and our leader.
You got something you want
to say about my sister?
Take it easy...
You mean you haven't
noticed anything about her?
No I haven't.
These guys were too well armed
and too well prepared to be out
for stealing a
simple truckload of shit.
I can't put my finger on
what they're really after.
I agree.
Something stinks and its not
just the truck or Haru's shorts.
But how's our sister involved.
I'm not positive that she is...
But today she was
an awesome captain,
and no leader that good
would be put in charge of this.
I think... She's lying to us.
So captain... is that right?
Uh... Hi, sis.
Now... You gonna try
and shut me up?
Silence me forever.
Or... do you just wanna
pick up where I left off?
Yo! I gotta say that Natsuko
has filled out rather well!
I love Natsuko. She's amazing!
Yeah, an amazing rack
of lambies on her!
Boobies, boobies, boobies!
Is that all you can think about!
What else is there?!
This is so dumb.
The next episode is
called "A Load Of..."
Shit! I forgot my box.