I am the one pushin' on ahead
just like you, yeah yeah
Won't you please hear me now
and give a name to
the demon in the desert
You can't help
but clench your teeth
As your heart starts
to tremble from the heat
Now stop it
It'll only bring destruction
Let's do it!
I killed an angel
The time has come
to stand and be strong
It's a sad history
hidden in a big story
That is the mystery
There's no way now of knowin'
Knowin' about what
tomorrow holds for me
So I just keep moving on
Living till the moment's gone
Forever just me
My mission
Ghost towns dot Kanto's
great desert landscape.
These villages are relics,
the only remnants
of ancient civilizations.
They contain valuable
natural resources
and priceless artifacts
that were left behind,
a mound of goods
as proof of life.
Nowadays people come
to these towns simply
to loot and cause destruction.
In an attempt to
bring some order
to these forgotten
outposts, each is numbered
in the order
they were discovered,
and subsequently discarded.
During excavations,
each ghost town is named
after the individual
or team that first finds it,
providing bragging
rights to those
who conquer the unknown.
We found one!
An unmapped ghost town!
So it was here after all.
Break out the booze, boys.
This calls for a celebration.
Check this sucker
out! It's aluminum!
I found titanium here!
This is incredible.
Just imagine what we'll
find below the surface!
Hell yeah!
This is virgin
territory, Kaizuka!
Gentlemen, we've discovered
the eighty-fifth
ghost town to date.
It had been twenty years
since ghost town eighty-four
had been unearthed.
Since then, no new
discoveries had yielded
so much as a fossil.
These three men had made
the biggest discovery
in a generation.
Then of course
we got shitcanned.
Run!
I ran for my life that day
and eventually passed
through the town gates.
The Guardian stopped
at the threshold,
not daring to venture
past the outer walls.
Why? I have no idea.
But I do know I was
lucky to have been spared.
From those ruins I only left
with my life and
a hallowed relic.
I had lost everything that day.
My two friends and
colleagues I had trusted
my life with for many years.
That was a decade ago,
but it seems like yesterday.
It changed me in ways
you couldn't understand.
I had no idea it
was that long ago.
Now you said that you found
an artifact in the ruins.
What was it?
A deteriorated computer
hard drive from the Dark Ages.
After cleaning it
out and tinkering
with it for a few days,
I found the time-worn
Game of Living on it.
I knew it!
There were plenty
more just like it...
but I didn't have
time to grab them.
What?!
A room with tons of money makers
like the Game of Living.
Plenty more just like it.
That game alone is
worth ten million yen!
Time to cash in
on that stuff baby!
I remember that room being
in the basement
of the tallest tower,
but then again I may be wrong.
It has been a decade
since I've been there.
Five of those years I
spent building my company
from the ground up and
distributing the game of Living,
the other five years
I've spent pursuing him.
Yet in those
five years I've made
no progress toward my goal...
I've started to believe
that killing him is impossible.
So all we need to do
is kill the Guardian
to get the treasure?!
I mean it's not like we
have to excavate the site.
We already know where
the goods are located.
It's so simple.
It's like we already have
the money in our pockets!
Right?
Ten million... Ten million...
ten million yen!
But doesn't that mean we'd have
to fight it out with
that gigantic monster?
You can take him, babe...
It shouldn't be
too hard since you're
Kanto Desert's number one.
You better believe
it sweetheart!
Just wait, I'll
tear him a new one!
Come on...
Okay then it's settled.
We should get started soon
but let's take a break...
My boobs are all sweaty.
I need to cool down first.
I'm gonna get
some rest over here.
Ahh, that's better.
I despise that filthy trick.
No peeping allowed boys.
You heard what the
broad said, old man.
No peeping!
I'm not trying to
sneek a peek, kid...
I'm merely keeping track.
The last thing
I want is information
about my treasure
being leaked to the world.
That's some smart thinking.
You expect me
to buy that stool?!
You'd be smart if
you did the same thing...
If she betrays me the ten
million yen deal is off...
It's all in the contract
if you read it kid.
Go ahead and stew if
it makes you feel better...
As for Junko I'll handle her.
You two start dinner...
we need to eat soon.
Let's see baby cakes ...
Where are you? You can't hide.
I just don't trust that old man.
Master, I kinda have a
theory I want to run by you.
Well I have my
doubts that the old man
is really after the treasure.
Why's that?
He knows how
deadly the Guardian is
and it already
killed his friends.
It seems too dangerous
to go after that treasure.
So, what is it
you're getting at?
Well...
I think it could be for revenge.
That's a terrible theory...!
Who the hell would
spend five years on revenge?
But weren't you even
listening to him before?
His two closest
friends were slaughtered
by the Guardian and
he barely escaped himself.
Plus the guy is a loner.
I think someone
like him gets a friend
once every fifty
years if he's lucky.
I know if I were in his shoes
I'd want revenge
more than anything.
Can't you see that?
You've put a lot of thought
into this haven't you...?
Lay it out?
Seeing as I'm not going to get
a dime of the ten
million yen reward,
I'm able to be objective
about the whole thing.
I've noticed that
you're pretty touchy
when Junko is around.
I get the feeling
you don't like her.
No crap.
Jealous much?
I can not believe
you just said that...!
What do you take me for...?
That may be the stupidest
thing you've ever said!
I can't stand how women like her
can use a couple
hanging lumps of flab
to get what they want.
She has no redeeming qualities
other than her bra size.
It's so stupid.
I hate girls like that!
You brat.
What the...
It has started.
Look at all of them.
Are they pirates or something?
This all feels off.
The Guardian!
Hey, Master! Look who it is!
That, scag...
That two timing scag!
Junko? I was wondering
where she ran off to.
What's she doing down there?
I thought she was with us?
Betrayal's all she knows.
She's been pullin this
job on us for a while.
I bet some rival interest
hired her when they heard
the legendary treasure
hunter was up to something.
That skank will pay!
This is it...!
The first new discovery in
this desert in over thirty years
and she's trying to
steal it for herself...
but there ain't no way
I'm gonna let that happen!
What a load of crap.
I'm going to tear her to shreds.
I'm watching you old man.
What are we going to do?
Let the Guardian take
care of the soldiers
while we swipe the goods.
Nice, chief.
That kid. I thought
he looked familiar.
It's those eyes of his.
Like a glint of light off
the steel of a sharp knife.
Part of me doesn't
want to trust him,
but perhaps that's just
what is necessary to slay
the vicious and
merciless Guardian.
What is that? A monster?
He's fast!
Everybody, fall back!
Keep holding him back!
I need more time!
I've got you now.
Did we get him?
I couldn't have asked for
a more perfect diversion...
Whoa that's the...
Hold up.
Huh?!
Hand it over Sluts McBoob!
Sorry but I'm no
slut little girl.
And this artifact
here is nothing.
There's plenty
more where it came from.
So why don't
you calm down and--
Shut up traitor!
You have a lot to learn kiddo.
It was clearly
written in my contract
that I could leave
at any time I wanted,
and I chose to
exercise that option.
Whatever.
If I said I
wouldn't hand it over
what would you do...? Shoot me?
I don't think you
have what it takes Kosuna...
Trust me you're gonna
need a certain level
of consciousness in order
to kill me in cold blood,
do this and you're finished.
You're such a cutie pie.
There you happy?!
Now hand it over!
If you want it you'll
have to come and get it.
Give it to me before I
pop those balloons of yours!
Not gonna happen.
This game is over kid!
You should never
throw down your weapon,
no matter what
someone says to you.
Does it hurt? Too bad kid...
I'm willing to do
whatever I have to do
to complete my objectives.
Some advice...
Unnecessary thoughts
will get you killed.
You can consider us
even now doll... Ciao!
You are one
pathetic apprentice.
Crap.
Looks like he finally
managed to kill them all.
With enough cold
hard cash anyone
can buy all kinds of help.
Yet that old
man took five years.
Of course it wasn't for revenge.
I didn't quite get it
at first, but I see it now.
Hey, you over there!
What are you fighting for?
Do you even remember?
There's no one left to
appreciate your abilities
and order you around.
Now come get it!
You're an amazing specimen!
I have to hand it to you,
you're really something else.
But this is the end!
Damn, I thought for sure
we'd get him this time...
I better not have to
wait another five years.
That won't be necessary.
You're still alive.
Huh, but I see you're
without the treasure,
so I guess that
means you failed.
Give me a break old man.
This was your
objective all along right?
There's no need to be afraid.
He's dead as a doornail.
Uh, you serious...?
Are you absolutely
positive he's dead?
Of course I am.
I got him good, see?
I guess you could say
I dealt the final blow.
Do you have any idea,
what it is you're sitting on?
Ah, well, kind of.
Kind of huh?
And you figured
this was more valuable
than the treasures found
in the ruin's basement...
Did you really believe
that I would want this
before a lifetime of wealth?
What, am I wrong?
You really are a spiteful kid...
I bet you don't
have many friends do you?
I have business associates!
I'm not kidding.
As a freelance
mercenary you hear
all kinds of
rumors and old stories.
For instance, toward
the end of the Dark Ages,
instead of using
humans to fight wars,
soldiers were manufactured.
Each one of these
soldiers had the strength
of one hundred men
and their dominance
eventually lead to
the demise of civilization.
Now I don't know
how true that story was,
but when I saw the
Guardian fighting that army,
I thought the other
treasures paled in comparison.
Defeating one of his
kind wasn't too difficult,
most of his
tactics were textbook,
but I can only imagine
the destructive force
an entire squad
of them could have...
Now be honest with me old man.
You've spent the last five years
testing the Guardian, right...?
To see if there's a
market for this nowadays.
In the last five years
I've worked in
complete secrecy...
Not even my son or my company
knew what I was doing ...
Look kid...
Just look at him...
Battered by the sun
and sand and even able
to endure the heat
from his own blasts,
he has survived the
last decade on his own.
His clothes are burnt
and stuck to his body.
His armor pitted
from countless gun battles.
All this without
any maintenance.
No repairs. He's
a perfect machine.
Add in that he
was most likely inactive
for hundreds of years
so he probably wasn't
even operating at
one hundred percent.
And still he managed
to display shocking
abilities at fighting.
His capacity for
growth is endless.
And the money to
be made. Boundless.
Scary.
That's right, kid.
I'm talking about you.
For the last
five years you've been
stringing along people
like me to battle him.
Getting others to
do your dirty work.
How many men have
died doing this...?
Tell me.
It's a small price to pay.
Think about the money here.
You know the world we live in.
What group wouldn't want
an army at their disposal?
They'll pay out the wazoo!
Oh hell's yeah!
That's awesome!
No unnecessary thoughts.
Watch where you're
shooting that thing!
No unnecessary thoughts.
Persistent little brat!
No unnecessary thoughts!
Damn.
Don't move.
You're pretty good kid.
So, why didn't you kill me?
Because there's no need to.
We're even now.
Take off your clothes.
I'm taking you to my master.
I lost! I lost!
And to a kid! Dammit!
I'm such an idiot!
I should have killed
you when I had the chance.
You annoying little piss-ant.
Keep your hands
where I can see them.
Yeah, yeah.
I understand.
I said strip.
Wow!
Evening boys!
I wasn't sure where
she hid her weapons
so I just had her
strip down for you Master.
Well well, what do we
have here, a nice little...
Damn you Junko!
You filthy traitor!
I'm sorry I'm sorry I'm sorry!
Excellent work Kosuna...
You've finally proved yourself
to be a worthy student.
Thanks.
All I had to do was avoid
unnecessary thoughts sir.
And you did well.
Now then.
That robot I killed
will be worth millions
but it's a threat to
the Oasis Governments...
I can assure you if
they find out about this
it will be the
end of your company...
They would go out of
their way to silence each
and every one of us
for what we've seen here.
If we make it
look like an accident
and kill you right now,
then at least the
rest of us will be spared.
That way, we could
at least recoup our costs.
If you were planning
to do this all along
I don't see the point
in killing the Guardian.
Why must we both die in the end?
A job's a job...
Besides it's no fun,
if I can't collect
on the ten million yen.
You're not going to kill me.
Maybe not now.
But we'll see
what happens if you come
after me down the
line wanting your money...
Believe it or not there are
plenty of people
that want me dead.
If you come after
me I won't hold back
against you or
your robot army...
However you should
know that I have never,
in my life broken a
confidentiality agreement
in my contract.
And I've never snitched
under any
circumstances, even torture.
Not that I expect the
most legendary treasure hunter
in all of Kanto to believe
a scumbag mercenary like me.
But I'm a professional
and that's what
keeps me in business.
Okay.
Question!
Go ahead, kiddo.
You plan on making
lots of these robots
and selling them right?
Precisely.
But, I heard that those robots
were the cause for
the last civilization
almost going extinct.
So what are you getting at?
Well after you make
your millions selling them
what if the robots really
do bring mankind to extinction.
Is it worth the risk?
If that's all it takes to wipe
the human race off
this planet then the sooner
it happens, the less
suffering there will be.
You're nuts.
After the demise
of the Dark Ages
treasure hunters like
myself began venturing into
this hellish desert to
find a better way of life,
or at least something
worth living for.
As years progressed
and more wealth
was unearthed people
began to flock here,
wells were dug and
towns starting forming.
Eventually it
grew into some oases.
That's why the Oasis Government,
which are just a bunch
of Johnny-come-lately's
who profess false safety
for this land, collect taxes
and make the rules
to suit their own needs.
They couldn't care
less about the people.
As long as they turn
a profit, anything goes.
I hate them for that.
So your plan all along was
to bring down the governments?
Just give me another ten years.
This desert will
look completely different.
We'll see...
Hey you're still going to pay me
to keep my mouth shut right?
Listen good, kiddo!
'Kay!
You'll be getting
ten million yen as well.
You did your part to earn it
so I'm giving you Junko's share.
You deserve it, kid.
You did a great job.
Oh come on!
Shut up prisoner
no talkie talkie...
Just be happy
we didn't leave you
in a ditch for
the vultures okay?
You mean you're
not going to kill her?
What would I do
with a dead chick?
But she sided with the enemy!
You can't let her
get away with that!
Kanta... If you're
still alive in ten years
why don't you look
me up...? I'll hire you.
I don't know...
By then who's to say
you won't be my enemy?
That kid.
I admire that
steely look in his eyes.
He's a tough
one that's for sure.
It's the same thing I used
to see in the mirror
when I was his age.
And with that
yet another nightmare
from the Dark Ages
made a step closer
to reviving itself.
Do these idiots
ever learn? Come on!
Start with one circle
Add one more circle
Then add one more big circle
Then a raincoat
blowing in the wind
It's actually a cape.
Whoa, don't forget
about the sunshade now
His heart is the
blackest in the desert.
His heart is black.
Shotgun is what he's gonna use
And then you've got
yourself a Sunabozu
He's on the run again
On the run again.
Just one more day and you'll see
He's got a job.
He won't stop
till tomorrow comes
He won't stop until
he gets the girl.
Until he gets the girl.
Get that girl!
Risking your life is
what you do, what you do
It's what you do
Yo! Desert Punk here.
Looks like I'm finally going
to get to juggle some gigglers!
Congrat's kid!
Hey, get your
hands off me you perv!
I'm not even sure
we can broadcast this!
Ah screw it!
Next episode,
"Compromising Positions!"
If you miss it,
Punk'll squeeze your nips!
Oww.