I am the one pushin' on ahead
just like you, yeah yeah
Won't you please hear me now
and give a name to
the demon in the desert
You can't help
but clench your teeth
As your heart starts
to tremble from the heat
Now stop it
It'll only bring destruction
Let's do it!
I killed an angel
The time has come
to stand and be strong
It's a sad history
hidden in a big story
That is the mystery
There's no way now of knowin'
Knowin' about what
tomorrow holds for me
So I just keep moving on
Living till the moment's gone
Forever just me
My mission
Legend speaks of a woman
who had observed man
from the dawn of civilization
all the way through to his
inevitable self-destruction.
She had rejected
him at every turn,
preferring to preserve
her own kind first.
Preferring survival
over what man had to offer.
Even in this age of the Great
Kanto Desert, she watches.
And she's still not
letting anything slip.
Calm down, it's just a rock.
It's not just an ordinary
rock, it's the inumeiwa...
That means dog, female, and
rock, which sounds harmless...
But the thing's as
cursed as King Tut's tomb.
Who's King Tut?
Oh, you're a moron.
The story goes, if you
try to move the inumeiwa rock,
you'll be cursed
by the Dogwoman.
Not far from the rock
there was a stretch of road...
I heard they were gonna
extend it that direction,
so I found that land,
and I bought it cheaper
than a used hooker...
I knew it was
too good to be true.
That kinda deal always is.
Yeah...
I knew I had to move that rock,
but every contractor I asked
slammed the door in my face.
It's liked
they were all scared.
I didn't know where to turn.
Desert people
are all superstitious.
Black cats, broken
mirrors. That kinda thing.
I figured that out.
So I went and hired the biggest,
nastiest oaf my money could buy.
What curse is he talking about?
The only curse here is the one
that I'm gonna throw
down on this stone bitch!
You tell her, brutha!
Hold on to your pantyhose!
Show that biatch why you're
the strongest in
the Western Oasis!
My brother...! I killed him!
It's... It's
not going to get me.
I can do this.
Just break the rock and
we get a new home to live in.
Just swing already, would you?!
When can we eat? I'm hungry.
Here goes...
My back ...
Honey! Are you okay?!
It was the curse...
I wanna go home!
No pathetic piece of stone can
defeat this--
My behemoth supertank!
Feel the shock and
awesomeness of my Kasumi II!
What the hell?!
Not the engine again!
It's... the... curse.
And I've hired dozens
that I haven't told you about.
Every last one of them failed
or buckled under the fear.
So what do you
want me to do about it?
Help me!
You're the desert's go-to man.
You head up the Handyman Guild.
You're my last resort...
I need that rock...
I need it obliterated!
Consider it done!
Just take a breath mint!
The inumeiwa rock?!
Yeah, but he's
willing to shell out
five hundred grand per person.
That's a ton of cash.
Balls no!
Uh...
Did you just say "balls no"?
Damn right.
The machinegun brothers don't
take on crapcrazy
jobs like that.
Yeah, it's not that
we're scared or anything.
Right. We just got,
uh, other things, to do.
Yeah. Other things.
Inumeiwa?!
What's the big deal?
I just need it moved.
My war wound's acting up!
Did you say the inumeiwa?
Yeah, it pays
five hundred thousand--
No, money don't mean nothin'
after the dogwoman
rips your balls off.
And believe me, my balls
have a lot of
work ahead of them.
Inumeiwa?!
Nooo!
Don't even mention
that cursed word around me!
Hmm.
You want me to remove
the inumeiwa rock, huh?
Please help me out
on this one Desert Punk.
It'll be worth your time.
But that thing is cursed!
It's where men and women
and children meet their doom!
But... it's just a big rock.
Great! That means you'll do it?
Gimme a break. It's
a little removal job.
They got grunts
for that kinda work.
Yeah, but all of those grunts
have already
chickened out on me.
What a bunch of pussies!
And...?
Don't forget about
your current situation.
Your reputation has
taken one hell of a hit,
but today that changes...
You're not washed up...
Go out there and prove
that Desert Punk's back...
The Demon of the
Desert rises again,
and he's not just
the best mercenary
in the Western Oasis,
he's the best mercenary
in the whole freakin desert!
In the whole freakin desert...
Trust me...
Only the Desert
Punk could swoop in
and pull off a
job of this magnitude.
That so?
We've seen that no ordinary
mercenary could do it...
But there is nothing ordinary
about you, Desert Punk.
Yeah, you're right...
this job should
be a flipping breeze
for someone with
my superior skills!
The curse!
It's already
started to take hold!
There's no such
thing as a curse!
Bartender...!
You chair is a piece of junk!
The complaint
box is by the door.
No...! It's the curse...
The curse of Inumeiwa!
What?!
What do you mean?
Why are you hanging back?
Still scared?
Course. Aren't you?
You'd be stupid not to be.
Then I'm stupid.
It's a mystical statue
created thousands of years ago,
during the age of darkness.
It's been cursed since
before man first
considered moving it.
So what?
It's so jinxed that no
one has ever budged it!
Not a single freakin'
person since the dawn of time!
Ha! Well, I ain't
just anyone, sister.
Try to remember who I am.
You can't lump me in
with all of those losers.
Thank you.
That son of a bitch.
Did he just call us losers?
Uh... I don't think
he meant us specifically.
I hope he doesn't hurt us...
Shut up!
If he actually
moves that damn stone,
we're gonna
look like jackasses,
and he'll rise above
it all as some kind
of hero they sing songs about.
You think we'll
ever live that down?
Pull it together, man!
Sorry about that,
I just get a little spooked.
We're taking a shortcut.
Right.
It's the curse,
the friggin' curse!
I can feel it!
There's no such thing.
Only babies believe that crap.
Is this an earthquake?
I hope not.
Where the hell is
that noise coming from?
That didn't feel too good.
The curse! The curse!
It almost killed us!
How many times do
I have to say this?
There is no curse!
Bad stuff is gonna
happen no matter what.
And every time it does,
you blame it on the curse
because that's all
you can think about!
If you keep
focusing on the negative,
that's all we'll get.
Look. You see the valley?
This place is
known for rockslides.
If you never heard of the curse
and you walked
through this place,
you still might get hit
by some of the falling crap.
Or you might not.
It's just a luck of the draw.
Do you get what I'm saying?
Do you?
Whatever. Let's keep moving.
All right, but I still
say this place is weird.
I was right! It's the curse!
There's no
stupid freakin' curse!
At least tell me
that you're kinda concerned
about the curse, chief.
Huh?
I'd feel a lot
better about being out here
if I just knew you
took the curse seriously.
Well I don't. It's
all a giant load of...
Dammit, man.
I just paid good money
to have this piece
of junk A/C unit fixed!
That dude replaced
all the busted parts!
Master!
I'm gonna find that repairman,
take every part
he fixed, pop them out,
and shove them
so far up his ass,
I'll air condition his brain!
Master! It's the
curse, you're gonna die!
Shut up already
and open your eyes!
It's not the curse!
It's a sandhole!
Ooh...
What is it?
My stomach is killing me.
Can I help?
That smells like death!
I just ate some
bad Thai food is all,
so don't tell me I'm cursed!
Master, you know what...
Not the curse,
it's not the curse.
I know it isn't.
I didn't even say anything.
Then what are you getting at?
Inumeiwa is
supposed to mean dog
and woman or dogwoman right?
Something like that.
I'm just wondering
exactly what a dogwoman is.
I don't know!
But oh, oh, since
they call her dogwoman,
she probably looks like a...
Like what?
Yeah, that's about it.
Ruff!
Mine is, I think,
quite a lot hotter than yours!
No...! It's not the curse...!
Now get off my case, shortstack!
You're trying
to convince yourself.
Nah ah!
Let's get a move on...!
With the A/C's
busted I don't wanna
be out here
longer than I have to.
Kosuna, let go of me!
You're acting like a scared kid!
What's your problem?!
I'll tell you
what your problem is.
They're everywhere.
All these signs
telling us to stay away.
Get your ass goin! Come on!
If you don't let go of me,
I'm gonna beat you
like a snare drum!
Well, we made it.
Ready to head on back now?
The inumeiwa rock...
It's nothing but a dressed
up piece of stone; look at it.
Stop saying stuff like that,
you're gonna
really piss her off!
Rock wearing a skirt.
You don't see that every day.
I never saw a
sandstorm blowing in!
It's... the... dogwoman!
Let's get it on!
What a surprise,
all the way out here.
The dogwoman...
looks like a dude.
I am a dude!
So, what's the
famous Rain Spider
doing on another
job I've been hired for?
Rain Spider? I've heard of you!
You're the collector
that roams the desert taking
not only the money from
men but their very souls!
And then you freakin' eat 'em!
From what I
understand, he'd rather
have a burger
and a beer like me.
Wow... Who'da
thought Desert Punk
and Rain Spider were friends.
We're not friends!
I guess after that hit
to your reputation
you had recently...
you've really felt the
need to get back on the horse.
You know, prove
that you don't suck
as much as everyone thinks.
I think you've had
more disasters than me.
Plus, you got yourself
a cute new assistant with
pretty pink hair.
Pink hair.
I know that went out of
style in like 1997 or so,
but kudos to her for sticking
with something outdated.
Whoa... Did you hear...?
He said I was cute
and he really likes
my awesome hairstyle!
Thank you!
Shut up!
Cut the crap. Why are you here?
The scenery.
Enough jokes. Why?!
I thought you would
have figured it out.
I'm going to
destroy the inumeiwa
before you get a chance.
Don't hate me.
Wait why?
Good ol' Ray
hired me the same time
he hired Mugenya
and a dozen others.
How can you blame me?
This is just business.
Ass clown!
What the hell?
This piece of
crap always jams...
Do you see that master...?
Everything's
being covered in mist!
That's not exactly what I see.
There's a party in my pants
and everyone's coming!
You shoot at me
again, and I'll kill you!
Why do I have to see this?
It's the curse!
It's tearing him up!
Possibly... but I don't think
he's putting up
too much of a fight.
But you did see it,
didn't you master...?
The creepy white mist
floating out from the rock?
You're delirious.
I didn't see anything.
But that's not
what should worry you.
We almost lost half a
million to this doorknob...
That's too close of a call
for us to make as a team...
From this point on,
we have to be more careful.
Your call, are we gonna
set a charge on that rock,
or shoot it from the ridge?
No...! No...! No...! No!
Shut your pie hole, kid,
and get that grenade
launcher out and ready!
Fine...! I'll take it then!
Please no!
Yeah, well,
I don't speak coward!
Did you say "coward"?
When did you get here?
We've been here the whole time.
And the three of
us aren't cowards!
Got it?!
No way I'm letting
you take my score!
Wow...! That...
looked like it hurt.
I... I failed... I hope
my sister can forgive me.
She must... It's not our fault.
It is the curse...
of the dogwoman,
No...! Please, let's go home!
Stop the madness!
Houston, we have a problem!
Let's bail!
Even the Machinegun
Brothers were chewed up
and spit out!
Which I'm so comfortable with,
I'll use it to
keep me warm tonight.
When I destroy that big rock...
the whole world will
know just how much I rock.
And how totally sweet
it is to be Desert Punk...
Then the next stop
is Sweater Puppy Station!
You're sounding crazy!
Why'd it get so
onim-om-uh, scary?
There wasn't a cloud in
the sky five seconds ago!
What's happening?!
That freakin' hurt...
Dogwoman you bitch-let!
Master, where are you?! Master!
That's the same
white mist I saw earlier!
Master, wake up!
What the hell
just happened...?
Huh...? I, feel
so squishy inside.
Lady, you're giving doggystyle
a whole new meaning!
You're smoking like a cigar!
Oh and look, you
brought your friends!
I don't like this.
It's like something's sucking
the oxygen out of the air...
And if that
thing keeps sucking,
then I'm gonna
end up pulled in, too!
That black blob!
It's master's plasma libido!
Please, try a little more.
'Kay.
Oh yeah! Sweet!
Course, I'd be drinking
anything you poured,
you filthy, stinkin' dog, you.
I'm pleased to meet your
standard of approval, Master.
Let's give the
mammary wagon a test drive.
No... Not yet.
You know you
want the sausage, baby!
This is so not right.
His superhuman manly desires
are actually
fighting the dogwoman!
He's an animal!
The libido plasma...
It's all sludgy
and black, like mud...
And that god awful
smell, it's like--
Nasty! Get it off!
Stop drop and roll!
If you really, really want me,
then you have to
try and catch me!
Are you putting me up
to a challenge, Ms. Dogwoman?
It's a battle between
hatred and desire...
It's hell... It's hell...
right here in
our desert it's hell!
There's no escaping
me now, pumpkin pie!
Time for me to eat you!
Yeah, about that...
I'll make you my trophy.
I love it when you howl!
Can't believe I'm alive...
But where did master go?
Oh my... You are
a sick, sick bastard!
Sorry, that happens
sometimes when I dream.
I guess I slept
through it. What did I miss?
A dream?
Was he just dreaming
everything that happened?
Would you look at
that beautiful sight there.
What the crap?!
The Inumeiwa Rock!
Looks like that
huge desert storm
knocked it all to pieces.
Speaking of
knocked to pieces...!
That's what getting
scared'll do to you boys...!
Right?!
I guess Desert Punk
has regained his title
of baddest stack of awesome
to walk these desert sands!
What are you waiting on, kid?
Let's get the hell
outta here and go collect.
You got it!
I wanna hurry up.
We got a sweet
half-million yen payday
waiting for us as we speak.
After that, all of the stories
about inumeiwa dried up,
like the desert itself.
But another rumor was birthed.
One about the man who eradicated
the curse of
the desert dogwoman.
The fame of Desert Punk
began to spread again,
and things got back to normal.
Which meant women
and drinking, of course.
But if that whole
scene that I saw back there
was something other
than a freaked out dream,
I swear, I might
just lose my damn mind.
I don't know if
I can handle that.
Well... Are you coming or not?!
Cripes, I don't know
what I've been thinking.
Desert Punk himself
is more dangerous
than some dumb curse.
But there's one
way in this desert,
and that's follow and learn.
I'll stick with him for
as long as he'll have me,
then I'll be on my own.
We'll see how
dangerous he is then.
Start with one circle
Add one more circle
Then add one more big circle
Then a raincoat
blowing in the wind
It's actually a cape.
Whoa, don't forget
about the sunshade now
His heart is the
blackest in the desert.
His heart is black.
Shotgun is what he's gonna use
And then you've got
yourself a Sunabozu
He's on the run again
On the run again.
Just one more day and you'll see
He's got a job.
He won't stop
till tomorrow comes
He won't stop until
he gets the girl.
Until he gets the girl.
Get that girl!
Risking your life is
what you do, what you do
It's what you do
Yo! Desert Punk here with a
serious question for you all.
How was Ray's
performance this episode?
Sucked.
I'll give you something to suck.
Ruff-ruff!
On the next Desert Punk,
"All That Glitters!"
I still think Ray sucked.
Yar, you suck.