I am the one pushin' on ahead
just like you, yeah yeah
Won't you please hear me now
and give a name to
the demon in the desert
You can't help
but clench your teeth
As your heart starts
to tremble from the heat
Now stop it
It'll only bring destruction
Let's do it!
I killed an angel
The time has come
to stand and be strong
It's a sad history
hidden in a big story
That is the mystery
There's no way now of knowin'
Knowin' about what
tomorrow holds for me
So I just keep moving on
Living till the moment's gone
Forever just me
My mission
Is that the village?
Yeah. That's our target...
Reclaimed Village Number 21...
Should be a
quick smash and grab.
Won't take long.
I can't imagine
living in this dump.
I can't imagine living in
any of these settlements.
They all look like crap.
But once they hit a water
table things will change.
You know how the saying goes.
"An oasis with
water is paradise."
If we have just one village
with water in our territory,
we'll be able to
live out the rest
of our lives in
the lap of luxury.
That's if these
morons strike water.
Let's come back...
Is our little weasel
still holding up?
Yeah. And when the day comes,
this crap-hole town turned
goldmine will be ours.
They're coming!
In the Great Kanto Desert,
Settlement 21 is a
well-digging village.
Poverty-stricken,
simple people built
this village in the
hopes of hitting it rich
by discovering a viable
and sustainable water supply.
In a desert. Good luck.
Geez, that was a long ride.
Is that me? I smell like cheese.
Okay...
I had heard stories before
I left but these people
are uglier than a
chorus line of rhino asses.
Anyone know where
I can get a shower?
This is soil from the well.
It feels damp.
Yes. It seems the deeper
we drill the more
saturated the soil gets.
That makes sense.
We also ran some tests
and there were no toxic
chemicals found in the soil.
Congratulations you did it ...
This is a huge
development for you...
People and money will
come pouring in now...
You can kiss this
skid row goodbye.
You really think so?
All right I'll take the job...
You can pay me later...
Once you guys hit water
my one time fee will be...
One Million yen.
Once the water starts
flowing one million
will seem like
pocket change to you...
Isn't that right?
Well, uh...
So we agree!
Why don't we discuss the
details over some water?
Let's see, we got
four large men wrapped
up tight inside of some
towels and carrying long
as well as short
ranged weapons...
Yeah... looks like we're dealing
with the Edo River Gang.
So just who are they?
You know, your run of
the mill gang of thieves...
In the Kanto area they're
no better than average.
You seem to be very
sure of yourself.
Well I cross-referenced
the information
you gave me with my
bad guy files I keep...
they're the only ones
that match the description.
You keep bad guy files?
I have to be prepared
for just about anything.
Uh...? What do
you mean anything?
Oh man...!
This tastes like
stomach bile, gross.
He just drank a
whole glass of water.
That's as much as
I've had in a whole week.
He said it tastes like bile.
If I drank a glass of water
that fast I'd throw up.
So what do you think?
Can you, take care
of our problem...?
Do we have a deal here?
A deal?
Of course I can take
care of your problem...
I'm only known in these parts...
as the Desert Demon.
Come on everybody drink up!
It's on the Sheik! His treat!
You guys need
to loosen up a bit!
You can drink all you want.
I'm here to protect the village
and you'll have
so much water soon
you won't know what
to do with it all.
Now let's party!
The Desert Demon!
We've heard so many
stories about you
here in this desolate
little village...
Your amazing razor-sharp brain,
and quick decisiveness!
Utilizing your
superior technique
you solve problems with ease!
You're a super mercenary
Mr. Desert Punk!
The ultimate... I am honored.
You're a funny guy...
What's your name there, pal?
Wano, I'll do
anything for praise...
Allow me to serve
as your right hand
man while you stay here.
Compared to outdoors
the temperature
in this room feels
like we're in an ice box.
And we have all
the water we want.
Damn right.
Not to mention this is
the sturdiest building
in the whole village.
Look out!
What happened?!
We need some help over here!
Get it off my leg!
Hey sweet cheeks!
There's a party
in my pants honey!
Everybody's coming baby!
Uhh! Get a sack!
Yeah, get lost fugly!
Mommy my throat
feels like it's on fire.
I'm so thirsty.
I'm sorry baby...
But there's nothing
I can do right now...
The man who is here to
save us drank all our rations.
Our food supply! What happened?
Don't you realize how much water
he's drunk today alone...?
An entire day's worth
for the whole village!
I know, I know...
but my hands are tied...
We have to give the
man what he wants.
What happens if he
drains our entire supply
and the well turns up dry?
And what about
that suck ass Wano?
He seems to have
forgotten that we saved him
from certain death
just cause he's been
brown nosing that Desert Punk!
Are you positive that kid
can protect us from
those thieves, Shiek?
What if he's full of crap?
There's no doubt in my mind...
He came highly recommended
by the Chairman of
the Handyman Guild.
Please be patient
with me on this.
It won't be much longer
before our efforts bear fruit.
You're just going
to have to trust me.
What are you doing with
that map of the village?
There's not much to it.
Wait I know!
You're planning your strategy
for when those thieves
arrive, aren't you?
I guess you could say that.
So what are
you planning to do?
Are you going to set up
an elaborate trap
for them to fall into?
The question is what direction
they will be coming from.
I know their
objective is the well.
They don't know
that we know about
their planned attack, or that
I'm here to defend against it.
And that is the best weapon
we can use against them.
Interesting...
When you consider
all of that stuff...
our best option
is to ambush them.
Where?
Here.
Ahh... That's great.
Well, I gotta go to bed...
Check you later.
I hate him.
Good evening, Desert Punk.
Well what do we have here?
They're not as big as Junko's,
but they have a
great shape to them.
Perky and quirky!
They're exquisite!
After all it's the shape,
not the size that counts.
Who am I kidding?
Bigger is always better!
No matter how nice the shape,
small zoombas just won't do!
Wait a minute!
When you think
about it, size is shape!
So that means I don't
have to give up either one!
Brilliant! I freaking
love boobs! Love 'em!
But are boobs everything?
No, the face must be nice too.
No matter how
juicy the rack is,
an ugly face will
just ruin it for sure.
Woah, look how bouncy these are!
Big ole tatas and
a face to look at.
Gotta get me some
of that yum-yum!
Sex!
Where you going...
so late at night?
I can't believe there's such
a smokin' piece in this village!
They should have brought
you to me sooner!
My name is Mariko.
I'm in charge of the
Settlement 21 Youth Corps...
I've been wanting
to have a chat with you.
My father the Shiek
seems to trust you...
but the rest of us here
have some serious
doubts about you.
What sort of doubts?
I think we need
to have a test to see
if you're really good enough
to protect this village.
Are you satisfied now
or should I beat the
crap out of you too?
You're strong.
Why wouldn't I be?
Plus your men
didn't stand a chance
because they
haven't eaten in days.
Let me make this clear...
With my reputation
as the best handyman
in the Desert on the
line I have a standard...
I follow through
on all my jobs...
But when someone does this to
me I tend to lose interest...
so prove to me that
you want me to help you.
Prove to you?
Let me do you!
Uh... All right.
But that offer stands only
if you successfully
protect this village...
And then you can
have your way with me.
And that's the only way.
If it means that we can
live a decent life here,
then Ill make that sacrifice.
That's the reason why
we've worked ourselves
nearly to death,
crawling around in the dirt,
and baking in the desert sun.
Don't worry baby, Ill be gentle.
Nice!
Desert Punk and
Wano took to trying
to have fun wherever
and whenever they could,
playing grab ass
just to pass the time,
but time was running out.
Then one day the
water the villagers
had long awaited came
surging up from the well.
With the water supply they
have dreamed of
gushing from the well
in extraordinary amounts,
the villagers celebrated
like they never had before.
And then, just as
everyone had figured,
the thieves arrived.
So the village idiots
hired Desert Punk.
This is gonna be a cinch.
Time to collect boys...
Lets cash in on that goldmine
and steal the rep from
that loser Desert Punk.
I don't know about you guys
but I'm not so sure
it was a good idea
to place all of us at
the front of the village.
Maybe but the women and children
were sent to
the Rationing Office,
so there's no one else to help.
I've heard the Edo River Gang
approach their victims disguised
as innocent travelers,
then once they're inside all
hell breaks loose.
Desert Punk said they'll come
from the East.
That's where we're facing, so we
can't miss them.
Where the hell
is that Desert Punk?
I thought he was
supposed to protect us!
He said he was going to do
some reconnaissance and left
with that bootlicker Wano.
You sure it's a good idea to
leave them alone?
We don't have to
worry about that side.
Why's that?
Because the enemy won't
be coming from the East.
They'll approach from there,
Skeleton City in the South.
You serious?
Of course I'm serious.
I'm the biggest bad ass...
in this entire forsaken
scum hole of a desert.
What are you talking about?
Hey Mariko! Honey!
What's wrong...?
Did you come looking for me
'cause you got lonely?
Or could it be because you can't
wait to get naked
with me, baby...?
My hasty little nympho, you're
so impatient it's adorable...
Oh sure, protecting the village
can come later...
but now I'll bury my face in
your sweet tatas...
I came over here to make
sure you weren't slacking off!
Well, I wasn't.
And what's the use
of putting everyone
on the East
side when they won't
be coming from
that direction?
You've left more than
seventy-five percent
of the city wide open!
Uhh...
you'll know why I
did that when you give me
a chance to explain
myself, Knokerbot.
This guy is a spy
for the Edo River Gang.
Wait no! Not the satchel!
Ah, I hope that hurts!
Anyone with an
ounce of brain matter
could have seen you
for the snitch you are!
I give... Okay... I'm a rat.
I had suspected there
was a leak somewhere in town.
But I never would have thought
it would be you Wano...
And to think we saved your life.
Pull your head out of your ass.
Maybe that's asking too much.
Dammit why didn't you let us
know sooner that he was a spy?
You amateurs.
If information was being leaked
to the enemy,
I figured I would work
that into our advantage.
What do I have
spell it out for you?
The villagers on the east side
are just a bait n switch.
Those jackasses will attack
from the south side and
victory will be mine.
So... you...
you were walking
around last night
in order to lay a trap for them?
Precisely.
Wait hold on...
You did all those terrible
things in order
to blind the spy to
your real strategy?
To convince him
of the wrong thing?
Heh?
Oh look at that face!
Those lovely eyes are begging me
to love them.
There's no doubt about it.
But I'm afraid of those eyes.
Hell I'm not ready to
settle down with one girl.
I can't even consider
spending the rest of
my life with just one
set of jugs to play with.
Wait.
I should probably just
do her once and that's it.
No need to lead her on.
And if I like it,
I'll bang her again.
So it's true?
I really got it right?
Don't worry, kitty cat.
This battle is already
ninety-nine percent won.
Your village will
be safe and prosper
into the future.
Can you dig me, baby?
What the crap?
That's the east side, isn't it?
Looks like the
attack has started!
Whoops.
Let go you fricking tool!
Wasn't the enemy
supposed to attack
from the South side
and not the East?
Uh, did I say that?
Oh Desert Punk! Please save us!
Where the hell were you...?!
You dumb bastard!
Yeah what about you?
Why didn't you
send the signal sooner?
The enemy... They came so fast.
There was no time to signal you.
You bunch of stupid, ugly,
good for nothing,
redneck, pole smoke--
You said they came on fast?
Damn it!
I guess this means
we're gonna have
ourselves an old
fashioned shootout!
Man this will suck the sweat
from the back of a monkey sack!
Rockets! No wonder
they were so quick!
Crap, crap, crap,
crap, crap, crap!
Just as we thought!
You really think we
wouldn't see through that?
This ain't our
square dance bitch!
Here's a little present for ya!
Kiss your balls goodbye!
I... just crapped myself!
Mommy.
Time for your shotgun Kolonic.
He's blinded our
spotter capabilities!
Crap, I can't see a thing!
That hurt.
Don't let that
scrawny prick get away!
After him!
They never found him.
Desert Punk had
vanished among the flames.
You are no longer the
leader of this village.
If you could just
sign this document.
It places all profits
and full ownership
of the village in our name.
This also means
that this one here
will become my pleasure slave.
Help!
The well!
What's the matter with the well?
It's, Desert Punk.
I can't believe it, he--
That, can't, be... My well!
What do we got there boss?
He's got it wired
with a crapload of C4.
Damn. We can't touch
it without setting it off!
The Edo River Chumps!
Glad to see you could make it!
You're all in for one hell
of an interesting show today!
That bucket contains more than
just a drum of C4.
I've placed a highly potent
and very dangerous poison
in the bottom of that bucket.
What?!
And here in my hand is
the triggering device to
make the damn thing go boom.
If it goes off,
the poison will ruin
the water table and
you can say goodbye
to your precious well.
You're dead you
giggly ass freak!
The contract I agreed to said
that I would
protect the village,
but it never mentioned anything
about protecting that
well, did it Sheik...?
And I'm pretty sure
that with the well gone,
this quaint little
village will have absolutely
no value to the Edo River Gang.
It's a foolproof plan!
You're insane.
I'll do whatever
it takes to stop you
from getting
your way. Dumbasses.
Please... You gotta help us!
Save the well...
We'll listen to
anything you have to say!
It's all we have!
Stop that stupid idiot
from destroying the
well and our village!
Spread his carcass
across the desert!
Start with one circle
Add one more circle
Then add one more big circle
Then a raincoat
blowing in the wind
It's actually a cape.
Whoa, don't forget
about the sunshade now
His heart is the
blackest in the desert.
His heart is black.
Shotgun is what he's gonna use
And then you've got
yourself a Sunabozu
He's on the run again
On the run again.
Just one more day and you'll see
He's got a job.
He won't stop
till tomorrow comes
He won't stop until
he gets the girl.
Until he gets the girl.
Get that girl!
Risking your life is
what you do, what you do
It's what you do
Yo! I'm Desert Punk
and I just pissed off
this whole village!
Speaking of, wasn't Mariko
stacked like pancakes?
Yeah, I'd like to
dowse 'em with maple syrup
and get my face stuck to 'em.
Hey, that's my daughter ya know.
She knows who her daddy is!
Next on Desert Punk,
"Wandering Lust!" Uhh!
Don't miss it!