I am the one pushin' on ahead
just like you, yeah yeah
Won't you please hear me now
and give a name to
the demon in the desert
You can't help
but clench your teeth
As your heart starts
to tremble from the heat
Now stop it
It'll only bring destruction
Let's do it!
I killed an angel
The time has come
to stand and be strong
It's a sad history
hidden in a big story
That is the mystery
There's no way now of knowin'
Knowin' about what
tomorrow holds for me
So I just keep moving on
Living till the moment's gone
Forever just me
My mission
The Great Kanto Desert.
During the day the
temperatures soar
above a hundred and twenty
degrees in the shade.
At night, it takes a nosedive
well below freezing.
These ruins are from a
forgotten civilization--
one that fell under
the weight of its own
thoughtlessness and greed
several hundred years ago.
They're here now only as grave
markers for the lost promise
of those who willfully
destroyed themselves.
And yet somehow their
descendants still managed
to survive this harsh
terrain over the years...
But these descendants
still have no idea
what the hell they're doing.
Namiko, get up!
Come on! If they catch us,
they'll kill us all!
Namiko, are you okay?
I'm hungry, mommy.
Can I have something to eat?
Are you kidding?
We'll eat when we're safe!
Honey, no!!
Tasty...
Let my mommy go, you creep!
Namiko!!
How cute...
I always wanted a family.
You can't get away from us.
I think the best thing for
you people to do is relax,
and let us take what we want.
But even if you don't,
we'll take it anyway.
Please don't violate me!
How could you do that to us?!
Making us think
your wife was hot!
Why would you try to protect
something that damn ugly? Man!
You have got
serious issues, loser!
Hey guys! You fellas happen
to be part of the Kawazu Gang?
Who are you?
Kinda small to be in
the desert alone, huh?
My size isn't the issue, chief.
You the ones who attacked
the oasis transport truck
at Water Station forty-five
three days ago?
You can take that question
and cram it up your ass!
Cram it up your ass!
Up the ass!
Yeah, that treasure you stole--
the owner hired me
to come take it back.
Yeah...? What are you,
some kinda cop? We kill cops!
We also kill bounty hunters!
We kill anything!
First off, no police officer
would dare make their way
out to this God-awful
Dutch oven of a place.
Second, bounty hunters just pick
on the weakest and smallest.
I guess I can't complain though,
I do get a lot of work.
Just tell me where that
idiot boss of yours is
and we can call our
business done.
Hell, I might even
let you walk away.
Aww... I offended them.
This is really getting old.
You think we used enough
bullets to finish him off?
Hey!! Look up there!!
Whoa! How's he
flying around like that?
He's that demon! I knew it!
He's gonna eat our souls!
It's the Desert Punk!!
What did you do...? I feel
like I'm dying over here...
It's my uber-badass
paralysis spray.
No taste, no smell, no color.
I'd say it works like a charm.
Y-You...
I have a reputation as a man
that will complete
any job given to me.
It's not a reputation
I intend to lose.
I worked too hard for it.
So why don't one of you three
slobbering nimrods tell me...
Where the hell is that damn
hideout of yours?! Huh?!
I ain't gonna say it again.
Fess up! I demand answers!
I'm gonna keep beating
you util you tell me!
Answer me! Where is it?!
Fifty-five, fifty-six...
Fifty-seven, fifty-eight,
fifty-nine, sixty. That's it.
Your lives today were saved for
two hundred thousand yen each.
That's a fantastic deal.
I hope to do business with you
again in the future. See ya!
This... was all
because I am weak.
I couldn't protect you
and now were dead broke!
Why'd I marry such a tool?
What? Those three wouldn't just
end up missing for no reason.
None of them are answering
their coms, either.
They were in charge of guarding
Sector Thirty-three in the west.
Those three jokers are too
busy playing around out there.
That makes three
jokers who aren't
getting any after
dinner pudding.
Sir! I'll personally
see to that!
Make sure their pudding
is on my plate tonight.
Pudding, pudding!
Sweet, luscious pudding!
Oh, it's worth living
and dying for!
Boss! I have bad news!
Yeah, what is it?
I found a letter
at the entrance.
At first I thought it was crap,
but it's signed by Desert Punk!
Mmm... Desert
Punk... How neat...
The reportedly small
mercenary who's going around
tearing up gangs using
magic-like powers...?
Sounds interesting... Read it.
Of course... Here goes...
"Dear Stupid Idiot Boss Man.
I am here to take your head.
You can fight me if you want,
but don't bother running.
It'll just wear you
out before I kill you
and that's no fun for anyone.
I've already busted up those
dumbass losers of yours,
and you're next, Jackass
Boss. With love, Desert Punk."
Uh-oh...
Yeah...?
Amazing. He calls Makoto
all those nasty things,
and he doesn't even flinch.
He's like a rock.
That's why he's the boss.
He's pretty damn cool,
if ya ask me.
And P.S.... Your mother is
nothing but a dirty whore.
My mother... ain't no... whore!
Boss is upset again!
I don't want to deal with this.
Careful...
What a face!
And those knockers!
Are you all right lady?!
Holy crap, please be all right!
I'll take care of you!
Sorry I kicked you.
I thought you were a scavenger
trying to steal my clothes.
Uh, okay. Look.
I just wanna know
what you're doing
all the way out here.
In such a sexy little number--
I mean, hot pants.
Look at you, you'll be
blistered and sun-poisoned
in less than a day unless
you have some more clothes.
Actually... I ran...
I ran away!
Please save me!
You're my new hero...!
You can finally save me!
Save you from what, exactly?
I was kidnapped and dragged
through the desert,
forced to travel with that
pudding-obsessed Kawazu guy.
I couldn't take it, so I found
a way out and I ran away.
What did those
bastards make you do?
I was told by Makoto that
I would make him vats
of his mother's pudding
for the rest of my life...
He'd whip me until
I got it perfect...
Man, that's pretty hot. I mean,
sure, the guy's gotta pay,
but damn, she probably
looked good making that pudding.
Please help me...!
I could die out here!
Don't cry.
Look, booby girl, I've got
some business to attend to
with those
Kawazu jerks, titties.
Let me take care of that,
and then, fun bags,
I'll escort you personally
back to the oasis.
How's that sound, milk mounds?
Wait a second...
Those three guards
aren't roaming around
out here anymore...
Hey, yeah, you must
be that guy!
She knows my work?
What's wrong with you, lady?
Are you okay?
It's the relief of finally being
safe since you're here.
It's overwhelming.
At this moment, this
woman truly needs me.
She needs every ounce
of courage I can muster.
She's relying on me
to save her very life!
She will suffer, nay!
I'll see it to the end!
It's over, Kawazu Gang.
What you've done to this
woman is unforgivable!
You're mine now!
I'm not quite sure I
know where they are.
It's around here, I know,
I just don't have specifics...
--y'know, like an address, or...
--Oh. It's right there.
Yes, yes it is.
There's no hideout here.
There's a balloon
tied to the ground.
Is that the Desert Punk?
He's smaller than I expected.
I've heard stories about him...
Some people say that he's
nothing but the desert sand
wrapped tight in those clothes.
The whole thing really
creeps me out, you know.
You're twice his size.
Calm down already.
Shit! He's looking right at us!
Then shoot him,
you moron! Shoot him!
Would someone please
shoot back at this jerk?!
What a bunch of freakin' morons.
You guys don't have
what it takes in the
grey matter department
if you're going to take me down.
You have to be smarter.
Fire! Fire!
Jeez, you'd think I
started this fight!
Dammit!
He's pinned down!
Don't lose him!
Well, I used up way
too much of my ammo.
I suppose I could tack it onto
the bill under 'incidentals'.
I am a businessman.
I have to consider the
bottom line, after all.
Which is fifteen hundr...
You guys are making it real
easy to shoot you right now!
He's only one guy!
Let's get him!
Remember kids,
a smart man knows
when it's time to run
like a little bitch!
What a fool!
He's running into a dead end!
Storm the building, men!
Wait, that's a--
Oh, shit!
You guys are bigger
losers than I thought.
That was good.
But 'good'... can't compare
to the legend of Desert Punk.
You were the one who
challenged me, but it turns out
you fell right into
my trap. How ironic.
That... is an ugly looking man.
Must've had it hard with all of
his 'Hulk Syndrome' and stuff.
I challenged you, huh?
Oh, you must be Makoto.
Of course I am!
Hey, easy there, big fella.
I just came here
to take back that little gold
necklace you're wearing.
And now I have to hurt you.
You have some nerve killing
off the Masami boys.
You're not gettin'
outta this one, Punk.
Not after what you've done.
How the hell do you think you're
getting out of here alive?
Make your move.
I'd love to see it.
Killing off? Get your
facts straight. They're fine.
I tied them up and tossed them
in a building somewhere, genius.
Who's your daddy now?
Tell me, who's your daddy?
My mother is not a dirty whore!
Uh, what?!
You son-of-a-bitch!
Don't play stupid!
We know you sent the letter!
Don't deny it! You signed
it yourself, crack head!
'Crack head'? Is he serious?
Well, that's it. I'm sick of
dealing with these turds!
Crap, it's camouflage gas!
Get him!
Alright, men... Cease fire...!
Go bring me the
pieces of that punk.
Hey, where'd he go?
I think we shredded
him with the gunfire.
So do we pick up the pieces?
That's what the boss said.
That freak is flying!
He's--He's a demon!
What's he gonna do to us??!
He's multiplying!
He is a demon!
Idiots! There's no such
things as demons!
Now, kill him!!
Whoo-hoo!!
Yee-Haw!!
Now that sideshow freak
is just dust in the wind!
Then what the hell is that?!
Boss! There's a dozen of him!
Your mother's a dirty whore...
--Your mother's a dirty whore...
You... prick!
Stop talking about my mother!!
Your mother's a dirty whore...!
Your mother's a dirty whore!
Stop saying that!
Got any ideas in
that small brain
about why they call
me Desert Punk?
My mother... is a saint, punk.
It's a... balloon?
No way!
He lost?
How the hell did he lose?!
That thing was
all flying around--
No human could do those things.
He's a demon!
He's the demon of the desert!
The legendary Desert Punk.
I own this desert, bitches!
Oh, it's tittie girl.
How ya doing?
You're amazing... I watched
you in action out there.
You really kicked
those fellas' asses.
Yeah, except that I didn't
see that explosive coming.
How could you? Oh, thanks
for grabbing this for me.
We work for the same client,
so I'm sure you understand...
This was just business.
To tell you the truth,
I really don't know what he
sees in that necklace anyway.
He's spent a boatload of
cash hiring people like us
to bring this thing back to him.
So--the--that--that--
that explosion that almost took
off my head--th-that was--
Yep... That was my handiwork.
It was too convenient to
pass up. Get crazy man Makoto
and the legendary Desert Punk
to destroy each other.
Makes my life much easier.
I'm Junko. And like you, I'll do
anything for cold hard cash.
Wait. You can't just take that--
You'll be seeing a lot more
of me, since I'm your
new rival and all. We're gonna
have some fun. Later!
What a freakin' bitch!
She's been playing me
since I found her all alone.
Me? She played me?
That is not cool!
Not cool at all!
The Great Kanto Desert.
Some of the fiercest and most
brutal people live day-to-day
in this scorching hell on earth.
But that's what it is.
A life of loneliness
and scavenging.
Junko, I'll find you.
You think you can just
pull the wool over my eyes?
No way. Not gonna
happen again, Tits McGee.
Walk on a man's pride and
expect him to just take it?
Uh-uh. You haven't won yet.
I finish every job I start
and I don't intend on
ruining my reputation
this late in the game!
I don't understand it, these
hardened desert people live
with inflamed pride... Which
seems to bite them in the ass.
You'd think they'd
learn their lesson.
It's a vicious cycle,
but... oh, well.
That busty bitch. The things
I'm gonna do to her.
But those knockers. Damn.
Those were nice.
She's gonna give
back what's mine.
I fought for it, I found it,
I stole it back.
Those jugs were huge,
though, weren't they?
Start with one circle
Add one more circle
Then add one more big circle
Then a raincoat
blowing in the wind
It's actually a cape.
Whoa, don't forget
about the sunshade now
His heart is the
blackest in the desert.
His heart is black.
Shotgun is what he's gonna use
And then you've got
yourself a Sunabozu
He's on the run again
On the run again.
Just one more day and you'll see
He's got a job.
He won't stop
till tomorrow comes
He won't stop until
he gets the girl.
Until he gets the girl.
Get that girl!
Risking your life is
what you do, what you do
It's what you do
Yo. What's up? I'm Desert Punk
and I'm here to tell you
that the next episode has
some nice knockers in it.
Do not refer to my
mother's loving bosom
as, quote, "knockers"!
Weirdo. On the next
episode of Desert Punk...
"Rock, Paper, Scissors!"
You don't want to miss it.