Is, is that really him?
You!
Wait! Where are you going?
Oh jeez!
It's moving again!
And so are we!
I don't think you're
gonna make it!
That was him...
No!
Kosuna, behind you!
Weird lights...
I wonder if they may
be some kind of strange
phenomenon predicting
future and tragic events.
Really, it's the last
episode. Can I eat now?
Kosuna!
Master...
Kosuna! Listen up!
Take a look at where you stand
in all of this right now...
You have to consider
your strength
versus your opponents...
what you want to do and what
you are actually capable of...
It's a lot to think about!
Don't get too intimidated!
Dumb kid... you
are not getting away!
My strength versus theirs.
What am I truly capable of?
What's my place in this fight?
Should I surrender?
Hell, no! I own these bitches!
What is she doing?!
She actually did it!
That's all I got
in me right now boys!
I'm gonna go find your sister.
You stay here and
finish what I started!
See you in a bit!
Did she just give us an order?
Yeah. She's Desert Punk's
apprentice through and through.
And we're still stuck
doing the grunt work.
Which is fine by me. Akio! Haru!
Let's show these
tank-totin'-tools
what the Machinegun
Brothers are packing!!
Yeah!
Is that you, Sergeant?
Chairman...
What's going on in here?
You're too late, Natsuko.
The whole facility
has been destroyed...
Everything ...
Every experiment is wiped out.
It's all over.
Everything's out of whack...
The lab's destroyed.
Only the Dark Ages
cannon is still active.
What kind of cannon?
Particle beam.
The crater we are deep
inside was cut into the earth
by this beam thousands
of years ago.
Then that light we
saw in the sky was...
It's an atmospheric reaction
as the device warms up.
We have to leave now!
It's too late.
You two need to
find some optimism.
This isn't my only laboratory.
But we have to fire the beam
to give those trespassers
what they deserve.
Nobody screws with Kaizuka!
You can't fire that weapon!
It's suicide!
mmmPoppycock!
The accelerated neutrons in the
beam will reach a velocity
great enough to vaporize every
living thing in this place.
Have you lost your mind?!
How is blowing all
of us up not suicide.
I have an escape route planned.
We'll be long gone
before the blast happens.
But we can't--
I didn't ask your opinion.
But why Kaizuka--
I've poured my soul into this
development and those bottom
feeders tried to tear apart
everything I've built.
They deserve every ounce
of pain coming to them.
That old dude has put on one
hell of a show for a long time.
And now we all get
to see the sticky turd
for what he actually is.
I didn't expect to see you here.
Well, here I am.
Oh, Matsu, I'm sorry.
We're pinned down.
I don't wanna die!!
I don't like this
anymore than you,
but we gotta play
this like the Punk would.
What? Didn't he come damn
close to killing himself.
Where am I?
Kosuna, you remind
me of a wet rat...
always looking for a
quick way out of the sewer.
Have some gun!
You're getting fast!
I don't have the time
to waste messing around
with a back-stabbing
panty hamster like you!
Whoa! Your master
vanishes for a bit
and you get a
nasty little mouth!
They're making this
way too easy on me.
What the--
I'm surprised you didn't
remember this trick
from last time!
Your new buddy
Desert Punk showed us
your one weak spot
a long time ago!
No!
Wolverines!
I'm, disappointed...
You've learned nothing...
all this time and you're no
better now than you were then...
I suppose that means...
that Kanto Desert's
baddest power babe,
isn't actually you.
Cause... It's... Us.
I bet you never thought...
That your life would end here.
What the hell?!
Why're you here?
Fulfilling my contract.
Rain Spider!
You've got razor wire
wrapped around your body.
Just like a fly, you're
trapped in the spider's web.
Try to escape, and the
web will only get stickier.
The point is,
keep your ass still.
Kosuna, where are you?!
Are you dead?
Those guys are still alive...?
I guess that means that
they were actually able
to bring down the Dragon.
What do you think you're doing?!
I can't go out like this.
I said don't move!
She's got a grenade!
Later.
Rain Spider, move!
I never thought you listened
to a thing Desert Punk said.
Shut up! I practiced
everything he taught me--
I was wrong.
That was one hell of a shot.
Now, go find your master.
But, you need help...
Go! Get out of here
before you die like me!
At least you didn't
hit me in the assets.
I can go out in one piece.
That's enough
for me. Run, Kosuna.
He won't wait around
here forever. Go...
Wait. What are you doing?
You're not gonna finish the job?
I know tomato juice
is expensive...
But it did save my life.
Too bad it couldn't do
the same thing for Kosuna.
I'm gonna miss
that scrawny leech.
Time for Junko to
hit the road folks!
I know those eyes too well.
They possess the same
look of rage and calmness
that mine did so many years ago.
Enough of your
hoity-toity words, geezer.
Get to the point.
Exactly what I mean.
I'll pop a bullet
through your jugular
in the middle of one of
your speeches if I have to.
You can't do that.
No kidding... What, did I do?
You're a liar, Kaizuka.
You and claim that all of
your work is for the people.
But the sad truth
behind all of this is
that you plan to take control
of the desert as well as
the people you
claim to represent.
No... You've got it all wrong...
The only reason we're here
is to ensure a decent future.
He's not anything
like you Desert Punk--
Move again and
I'll shoot you in the face.
Kaizuka's money still
isn't enough for him.
He can only think of himself,
which doesn't leave
any room for you guys.
What happens after you kill me?
Any big plans?
How 'bout a vacation?
No amount of talking's
gonna slow me down.
Or maybe you and
your little girlfriend
can start a family together?
Kanta!
Letting you stay alive
was a huge mistake,
and I don't plan
on making it twice.
Wow, you're cool.
Kaizuka may be a
self-involved ego maniac...
Natsuko, what are you saying?
I'm saying--
That at least he's
not so heartless
that he would betray those
closest to him like Kanta would.
I can't believe you
fell for my oldest trick!
Even Kosuna sees
through that one by now!
And if that one got you,
I know you won't
see this coming.
Take her.
Human beings should not
waste life, for it is precious.
How the hell did this
thing get a hold of me?
He's got a cloaking device.
So...
What do you say we put
an end to this right now?
You're going to die down
here with us, you know.
I'm not gonna die... Not today.
You might not have
a choice in it.
We'll see.
Natsuko!
Here we come!
There she is!
You made it!
Punk is here too?!
Whatever, just shoot!
Junko let them get away!
Slow down man!
Mekori, I need some
help over here! Come on!!
Affirmative.
Master!
Our bullets are useless
against that wall of a robot.
What are we going to use?
Are you okay Natsuko?
Yeah, I'm fine.
But we have to get out of these
ruins before they blow.
Master, what's going on?
The coast is clear.
Good. Let's bail
before we get lit up!
I'm right behind you!
Don't have to tell me twice!
It took you long
enough to get up here.
Master? Master!!!
Hey-o!
Found him!
They're all over the place!
Why won't these
dudes leave us alone?!
And these dudes ain't balloons,
if you couldn't tell.
Kanta, you son of a bitch!
I suppose we don't
have much of a choice.
Then let's tear 'em up!
They'll either kill us now
or later, and I hate waiting.
No, don't!
Ow, that hurt.
What are you doing?!
Ciao bitches!
That guy sucks.
Aw, Let him go...
He's just a cockroach.
Master?
We thought you were dead.
From the second I saw
you again back there,
I knew I had to tell you things.
Things that I didn't think
I'd ever have the chance to say.
I don't know what's
happened to you,
but you need to
know this about me.
I've always considered
you my savior.
You see, I make
mistakes today the same
as when you and I were together.
The difference is that back
then I all I had to do
was follow orders.
Now I have to give them,
and sometimes I don't
trust myself with how I think.
And I thought that you
sacrificed your life--
And that's where you're wrong.
I wasn't interested
in saving anything
but my own pale ass...
I was using all of you...
I needed an easy way
out of that place
and you guys were there.
Then I screwed up.
I got caught...
But I flipped my situation
and joined these guys.
You sold out the
people you know best
to get in bed with the bad guys?
Is this a war?
You can call it what
you want, old man...
But you know what it is.
There's been pressure
on our boundaries.
Maybe you're
underground mercenaries
or the dragnet elite,
I don't care.
I'm just here to stop you.
So you're just here
to cash in my body
for another step up the
government's military ladder?
Anything goes out here...
This is a war, right?
You're going to use us
to take over the oasis.
That's your plan.
Yep.
Where are you, Kosuna?
I'm sorry... I'm sorry
I dragged you all into this.
No apologizing!
Yeah, sis!
I'm proud that I got to fight
this battle with you!
We followed you into Hell,
and we'll follow you out.
Thanks guys...
Kosuna!
Yeah, what!
I wanna give you a choice.
What you've shown today says
that you might have
what it takes to do this.
You can come over to my side,
but you have to tell me now.
Huh? Oh, uh... I uh... well...
I know it might be hard...
War can be confusing.
But know that
inside this confusion,
you can finally become Kanto
Desert's baddest power babe.
Master.
Yeah?
I have to know something...
The fire that burned
down Matsu's store...
did money from your
pocket pay for that?
Oh... Yeah, that.
If anyone had known
I was still alive...
there would have been
some big problems.
After I went back for the winch,
I didn't have much of a choice.
I thought about feeling bad
about it, if that matters.
What are you doing staring
down that little girl?!
You were supposed
to kill Kaizuka!
Yeah... I'm on that.
Mitz, you stupid,
piece of trash!
Show me what you're
made of you pansy!
Do not move.
You slime...
I'm gonna kill your father.
Kosuna... Oh, no...
Where's your winch?
Now we have to
deal with this kid!
Hulk Syndrome.
Now!
What did, you do?!
I bet you didn't know,
that Matsu's winches
could do this!
Kosuna...! You are in
so much trouble young lady!
I'm so clever.
Anyone wanna leave.
But where do we go?
No clue! But we gotta move fast!
I am Rain Spider,
Savior of the Sands
and all her people!!
This is it!
That truck is our
ticket outta this place!
Oh... Okay.
Get into the back, hurry!
They actually had a plan-B.
I never expected
it with that group.
But they did leave one behind
which means they must
not be that organized.
Master.
I'm not switching sides.
From now on, you're my enemy.
That's your decision...
Can you live with it?
I just saved your ass Punk.
I'll follow you wherever you go!
You have to do
whatever's necessary.
Idiot! Why did you
shoot at that thing?!
I'm sorry!
No...! Please, let's go home!
Stop the madness!
You know what I really want?
A 308 caliber assault rifle!
It's so heavy...
I'd be useless after an hour.
You, brat.
Thanks!
Thanks, master!
Master!
Master! Master! Master! Master!!
Mitz! We're going!
And still there's
that other voice
in my head that
tells me, "You're stupid.
That's your master.
It would be so much
better over there with him."
Betraying us the way
he did was something
very much in character for him.
I don't know how good that is.
As bad an apprentice
I was to him at times,
he said I'd gotten better.
But if I went with master,
it would be another lifetime
of being his little sidekick.
That would ensure
that I'd never become
the baddest power babe
of the Great Kanto Desert.
Which I can't let happen.
Let's get out of here, Mekori.
Time is up.
That was the moment it happened.
The moment the dead
of night gave birth
to mid-afternoon in
the Great Kanto Desert.
A place where the brutal and
the righteous are brothers.
The Great Kanto Desert.
During the day
the temperature soars
above a hundred and twenty
degrees in the shade.
At night, it takes a
nosedive well below freezing.
These are the ruins
of a civilization--
one that fell under the weight
of its own thoughtlessness
and greed several
hundred years ago.
It is now simply a grave
reminder of the lost promise
of those who
destroyed themselves.
The Great Kanto Desert.
The fiercest and most brutal
people in human history
live day-to-day in this
scorching hell on earth.
It is a life of loneliness
and scavenging.
Come again, will you?
Today, these hardened people
of the desert live
with bolstered pride...
Which also seems to
be one of the things
that brings about
hard times for them.
It's a vicious cycle.
But oh, well.
That's the way it goes, I guess.
And these people sure
aren't changing... dumb-asses.