Goodbye, Kanta.
This may be the last,
time you and I ever lock eyes.
Come here and gimme some of
that before you go... aggeggh...
I guess I should be thankful
that they're not
going to execute me...
Of course, compared
to years in prison,
a day in the electric chair
might not be so bad.
I'm not putting any of
the blame for this on you...
You've always tried to keep
me safe. You're so sweet...
It was a good effort.
But now I'm off to jail.
I told you to be
a man and win me over
with your charm and dignity.
I said I'd be your slave.
I'd do whatever you wanted.
And here when I'm ready...
You get me sent to jail...
For a little corporate
espionage, dumb-ass.
Say goodbye to these
roller-coaster rockets
cause you'll never have them.
Hope you have a
nice and lonely life!
Nooo!!
I was supposed to take
that left at Albuquerque.
Master. Would you
get over it already?
You've been pouting
like this for a week now
and it's really starting
to get under my skin.
Face the facts. Junko is toast.
Good riddance.
She's in the slammer
for corporate espionage,
so she's gone for a long time.
That's if she's not dead already
from the inhumane conditions
and constant torturing.
Uh?
You've been acting like a
frantic little idiot for days...
You digging those
foxholes not only
wastes time and energy,
it pisses me off.
Lay off of me...!
I've been really bored.
We don't know if those tanks
are gonna come back for us...
Junko may have ratted us out
and if that's the case
I want to be prepared.
You're stupid.
If the government
really wanted to capture us,
no defense we could dream
up would ever be enough...
We could never win
that battle by ourselves.
My contract was stamped
with a government seal
and issued by Mugenya.
It should have been
binding in this region,
but they ripped it up like
a brothel sign-in sheet.
Watching them
destroy my contract
without an explanation
is all the proof I need
to see where I stand out here.
Our existence in this
desert is meaningless.
We're like poo in a monkey's paw
being thrown around the desert
at the government's discretion.
They can't be all bad.
They still supply a
lot people with food
and the fuel they
need for generators.
Anyway, it's not gonna do me
any good whining about it now.
But if I ever see those
colostomy bags again,
I'm gonna give them
a piece of my mind.
Huh?
I didn't know there was
a Chinoike artifact
investigative unit.
Yes, and I'm the Captain. Ikeda.
So what's your job?
Just wandering around,
searching for artifacts?
Well, yes, most of the time,
but right now...
I'm searching for
a missing person.
I thought all the
artifacts worth anything
had already been
dug up and cashed in.
The ones that are worth
something have been,
but there are still plenty
of finds with academic value.
So who is this person you
want us to find for you?
Is it a business partner?
Someone you have to kill?
The man who
broke your back door.
Very funny but no. This person
is with the military.
Military? You mean he's with
the West Oasis Government?
Yes that's right.
Our investigations can take
us to dangerous territory,
so we always have armed
security as an escort.
We were excavating
a deserted village
when we came under attack.
Many of my men were
killed in the process.
I tried, but I never
got a good look at who...
Get down!
Fuyo?!
Uh, what's going on?
Are we alive?
Punk! What are you doing here?!
Not these dudes again.
I sure as hell didn't
come out here for the view.
I'm on a job.
What are you guys doing?
I thought you were
taking some time off.
Keep it together.
It's Natsuko... she's...
she's gone missing.
Bummer.
It happened during
a covert operation,
so according to the authorities,
she isn't officially
considered missing.
And since it's not official,
the bastards refuse to
send out a search party.
That is something.
A freaky coincidence
considering my client here
is searching for a
missing person as well.
Ikeda these guys
are the brothers
of Sergeant Kawaguchi, the same
Sergeant you're looking for.
Really?
No way!
The way I see it...
Since we're all looking
for the same chick,
we'll cover more ground
and do it faster
if we work as a team?
Whattya say?
Come here you little bastard,
bring it in to poppi!
So I take it you three were
conducting your search in
and around this city?
Yeah.
Then you were working off
some pretty crappy intelligence.
What the hell you
trying to say huh?
It's, it's just that...
You're looking for her
in the wrong place.
Sergeant Kawaguchi
wasn't abducted in the city.
She was taken down below.
Below?!
Oh that's nice.
A hidden door!
Aw, dark smelly holes scare me.
This hidden entrance
is so top secret
that not even the upper echelons
of the government know about it.
If any of you leaked the
whereabouts of this place--
Blah, blah, secrets!
Enough with lecturing!
Now, lead the way, Ike!
I just pooed in my suit!
Don't just stand there.
Let's follow him.
Wait for me!
We're coming Natsuko!
You sure I shouldn't stay behind
and keep an eye on things.
Shut up.
Sawada. Their heat
signature has disappeared.
We are unable
to continue tracking.
What?
There's no way those
men could just vanish.
You mindless fools!
Humans cannot and
do not disappear!
They either have a device
to cloak their heat signature
or they're beyond the
range of your sensors.
Understood.
We have learned now.
We're going after them.
Wow!
Freaky! What is this place?
I can't believe something
this ginormous
is underneath the ruins.
Incredible isn't it?
We're three hundred
meters below the surface
and the best part is
that the government
has no idea it exists.
What you are looking at is
the legendary Underground City
of the Dark Ages.
No shit.
This place is the whale's balls!
There's tons of
metals and plastics,
even materials
I've never seen before.
I gotta figure a way to
haul all of this outta here.
Hell there's enough
of a fortune here
for me to afford a
harem of slutty women
in every village
across the desert.
And you're only
seeing one percent of it.
All of the other
ruined sites have
been picked clean
of their good stuff.
Yeah wait until everyone
else in the desert
hears about this place.
Master, take a look at this.
What is it?
It's a rock.
Look closer.
December fifteenth,
three thousand twenty six.
Those are survivors' notes.
Those who became separated
from their loved ones
would leave notes
to let the others know
that they were safe.
You can find them
all over the place.
Parents looking for their kids.
Lovers praying
for a safe reunion.
And some just asking why.
Check it out.
This is soot from a fire.
You'll notice the ceiling
is covered in burn marks.
It appears that
this entire tunnel
was engulfed in
flames at one point.
I wonder what could
have happened down here.
Whatever it was a lot of people
lost their lives in this tunnel.
I read this cool
book recently...
It said that in the Dark Ages
there was a civilization
capable of sending
people to the stars...
Something really horrible
must have happened
to cause the extinction of
such an advanced society.
I wonder if the
guy who wrote this
was ever able to
reunite with his family.
Kosuna, it doesn't matter.
It happened, like,
a million years ago.
Wait for me!
I've seen one of
these things before...
It was in that same book...
What was it called?
A train!
Heeeey!!
Bouncy! Bouncy!
Wow.
This is so cool!
Backward, forward, backward,
forward, backward...
This thing looks like
a form of transportation
that was obviously
designed for long-haul travel.
So the Underground
City must be huge.
For many years now
I've been researching
the Dark Ages
and its hidden cities.
And with all the data
I've compiled it seems
very likely that these
underground channels
span the entire Kanto Desert.
That would make this one tunnel
over a thousand
miles long, right?
Correct, though many large
portions of it have caved in.
Toward the end of the Dark Ages,
people started to
take refuge underground
to escape an unknown danger.
Yeah that's a
comforting thought.
So they moved down
here to be safer?
From what? I see they
did a great job of dying.
Alright Smarty McThinks-a-lot.
We gotta get our
game on and find Natsuko.
Just follow me.
Mister Desert Punk sir...
Have you ever been
inside the West Oasis?
No, but when I was a kid
my father tried to get us in.
And that sucked...
We were turned away when
we got to the entrance.
It looked then kinda
like it does now.
The front gates were so enormous
they actually frightened me.
The place was so huge it made
me want to puke my lungs out.
Then there were those shanty
towns just outside the gate.
They looked so pathetic
against the oasis walls.
That's the place formed
by the workers who
built the Oasis, right?
They live like that and they
still work for the government?
Yeah. That's
Central Watering Station.
It's where all the mindless
government lackeys live.
It's a real poop market.
That poop market happens
to be my hometown.
Oh It's lovely.
Whatever it doesn't
matter where I'm from.
Tell me, do you happen to
know what's inside the Oasis?
Well from the rumors
I've heard over the years...
it's some kinda
huge underground city.
Underground?
It's a sprawling
subterranean complex,
enormous even by
government standards.
Our leaders operate
out of an ancient
buried facility submerged
three thousand meters
below the surface.
Its size is so vast that they
only utilize half of the space.
Most of the unused portions
are still unexplored
even to this day.
Isn't that amazing?
Yeah, no... Just thinking about
such a place gives me
an itchel on my satchel.
There was an incident that
happened about ten years ago.
In the deepest regions
of the West Oasis
a surveying
technician became lost.
The area he was in
was an elaborate maze.
Once he got turned around,
there was no hope for him.
Then one week later...
the surveyor was found.
He was discovered
over fifty miles away
from where he had
originally become lost.
Wait a minute.
He was found at
the same entrance
we just used to get down here.
Inddeed Mister Desert Punk.
You pick up on these
things rather quickly.
What you're saying
is that we're sitting
on the back porch
of the West Oasis.
What?
I came to this
area ten years ago
to begin my research
on the ruins.
Before he succumbed
to his dementia,
that surveyor told me
about the existence
of this underground city.
You mean the poor surveyor died?
Yes.
Due to the shock of
being lost in the dark
for a week with
no water or food,
his health was beyond
the limits of medicine.
We held a service for
him once he passed
and buried him
here in the tunnel.
Hold on now... you never
sent the body to his family?
Um, no we didn't. Why?
If news of the surveyor's death
went public then everyone would
know about your discovery.
Dick!
You set us up...!
You conniving,
bottom-feeding jack-hole...!
What in the hell have
you gotten us into?!
What are you getting
all bent outta shape for?
Try opening your eyes, Fuyo ...!
We've been wandering
around a back entrance
even the government
doesn't know about...
That makes us terrorists!
He's dragged us into his twisted
anti-government movement!
Even though I work
for the government
and live in that shanty
town as you call it...
my personal and political
beliefs do lie elsewhere.
You hate the government
and you're my sister's enemy!
Which makes you my enemy!
Spill it, you troll!
Were your terrorist
friends responsible
for Natsuko's disappearance?
No! Not exactly!
Hey...! Give back my rifle!
What are you doing??!
Please no!
Come out come out
wherever you are!
How was he able to see us?
We're over six
hundred meters away!
Situation report.
Minor damage confirmed.
We have been fired upon
and have yet to receive
instructions for this situation.
Awaiting new orders.
Come on!
Do I have to spell out
every little thing for you?!
Since following them
has obviously failed,
it's time we show some force.
Now go capture one of them
so we can get some information!
That's your order!
Not so fast!
Where'd they come from?
I can't allow
anyone to leave here
with information
about this place.
Shoot them.
What the...!
Whoa. Looks like we have
more company than I expected.
It's a full on battle!
I wonder who a...
We've been following
you my brothers.
Natsuko!
It's true.
We heard that
you'd been abducted
so we came all the way
here to rescue you.
You're not hurt, are you sis?
Your sister's just fine.
This was a crock of
shit from the get-go.
I got your number now.
To think that all this
time I thought you
were just some worker bee
for the government...
Talk about biting the
hand that feeds you!
You're a rebel with
the rest of these guys!
A no good terrorist!
Well, I was born and
raised in the desert.
Listen up.
I don't care if you
have to slaughter
every single one
of their soldiers.
This is your time to show
them what you're capable of!
Use the combat skills I've
taught you and blow them away!
Affirmative.
Oh no!
Whatever you do make sure
you capture their
commander alive!
I need to find out how
he's connected to this.
What are these things?!
Question sir.
How do we differentiate
between the commander
and his soldiers?
You actually need me to give
you instructions on that...?!
He's the cowardly guy
in the back giving all
the friggin' orders!
Just get your programmed
butts out there
and capture them all!
What's with this elaborate
and long-winded effort
to try and recruit me
into your alliance?
I can see how you'd
want me in your group
with my super reputation...
I have the ability to chew up
my enemy and spit 'em out!
But help me understand
why you chose
to show me this tunnel,
your big secret,
before you knew
if I'd join or not...?
What the hell were you thinking?
It wasn't my decision.
Say what?
I don't trust you one bit Kanta,
and I don't want you
to have anything
to do with our alliance.
Someone else insisted
on you coming here.
Oh really.
What does he gain
by showing me this...?
And who is this nutjob?
You'll find out soon...
I want to make something
very clear to you Kanta...
My fellow soldiers
and I are not here
for our own personal gain...
Our objective is to make the
desert a better place to live.
If the desert inhabitants
united and helped each other,
we could create a
world where the weak
and poor can live without fear.
We wish to create
such a society,
and we can do it with your help.
Uh oh. Wrong note.
That's just the kind of
thing he hates... Oh well.
Himuro, Himuro, answer me...!
Shusaki what is happening
to the right flank?!
Stryker, sir. The entire
second unit has been...
Capture them all.
This isn't good...
Damn government army.
Why did I even bother with them?
Sergeant Kawaguchi.
We're retreating.
Roger that Stryker...
I have Desert Punk
detained and ready.
Where'd he go?
Master. Are you just
going to ditch Natsuko?
Idiot...! We owe nothing
to the government
nor to Natsuko's
little rebel faction...
Screw'em to the walls I say!
A solid point
but not very polite.
Yar.
Ahh... Wait!
Those things look familiar!
Usually have to hide those!
Inconceivable!
How the hell could he
have fallen for that?!
Sametsu, what's your status?
Come in! Come in!
Damage is minor.
I will continue advancing
the attack at once.
He has some thick armor on him,
but he seems like
a real dumbass.
So do you.
Natsuko, what are you doing?!
I would prefer that he walk
himself out of this tunnel...
but your friend here
can not be trusted.
I guess you're right.
Hey this is the coolest dude
in the Desert, Stryker!
We're gathered here today
to remember Desert Punk's...
Cram it! I'm not dead yet!
Ahh, bummer.
Master becomes a shooting star
in the next episode,
"A Raw Deal".
Miss it and I'll spank you!
You know I like that.