I am the one pushin' on ahead
just like you, yeah yeah
Won't you please hear me now
and give a name to
the demon in the desert
You can't help
but clench your teeth
As your heart starts
to tremble from the heat
Now stop it
It'll only bring destruction
Let's do it!
I killed an angel
The time has come
to stand and be strong
It's a sad history
hidden in a big story
That is the mystery
There's no way now of knowin'
Knowin' about what
tomorrow holds for me
So I just keep moving on
Living till the moment's gone
Forever just me
My mission
The M40A1 sniper rifle.
7.62 caliber rounds.
Fiberglass stock and rubber
mounted ten power scope.
Effective range of
one thousand yards.
But crap, it's two-hundred
twenty-five thousand yen!
Man, that's a little
pricey for a reproduction!
Uhh! The collectors are here!
W-Wait a minute.
The deadline's
still a week away.
Who the hell's knocking on my
door at this hour?
Well hello there.
I recognize those
titties! Junko?!
What's so funny?
You're just a kid!
This is Kanta.
A freelance mercenary.
Why the hell are you laughing?
Just the thought that
the famed Desert Punk
is some kid,
it's just too hilarious!
Oh no! Now everyone's
going to know!
He's become rather famous lately
in Kanto known as
the great Desert Punk.
What the hell are
you doing here?
I have a job if you're
looking for some cash.
Uh, what?
I did some poking
around for myself
and found out that you're
in debt up to your ears.
What?
Who the hell told
you about that?!
He has failed in
his last two jobs
and started taking
on the debt of others.
Each failure was directly
linked to a woman.
The Chairman filled me
in on all the details.
Mugenya, that
dirty son of a bitch.
Who do you think you are going
around town asking about me?
You owe me big time now woman!
Hey watch it happy hands!
Feels like my birthday!
I charge ten thousand
yen for touching these.
And since I know you don't
have a dime to your name...
you better keep your hands
to yourself little boy.
So how much do you owe?
Let's see,
one million six hundred
ninety three thousand four
hundred fifty two plus six,
carry the one...
Around three million yen.
I'll pay you six.
Whoa!
Okay.
I'm your man. Whatever you need.
Booby sandwich... with
a six million yen dessert.
Once I pay off all
of my old debts...
I'll be able to buy the
sniper rifle of my dreams...
And I'll have enough left over
to have knockers like these...
everyday for the
rest of my life!
The dream Kanta had that night
was a splendid one indeed.
I wish I could have had
one like it... Anyway...
Hey Desert Punk!
I seem to remember you saying
this would be a piece of cake.
Yeah, piece of cake my ass,
we wouldn't even be in this
mess if it wasn't for you.
She's your damn friend.
What the hell are
you talking about?
She lured you in with
those massive jugs, too!
Th-There it is!
Nothing can stop that thing!
It travels like a
storm through the desert.
I've heard that it
burns anyone in its path
to a crisp, leaving
only ashes behind!
It's the mightiest,
most indestructible
and fully armored tank
in the entire Kanto Desert.
No! It's a cold blooded
killing machine resurrected
from the pits of hell
and forged in steel!
Fire Dragon Kong.
Don't plan on getting away
from me this time Junko.
I see you've hired a band
of imbeciles to help you out.
They're useless against
Kong, you know that!
You better take these
so called imbeciles
very seriously,
or else you'll be sorry.
Don't listen to her!
She's kidding!
She jokes all the time!
These four guys
have more courage
in their pinky toes than you do,
hiding inside that
huge pile of junk.
No we don't!
We're a bunch of cowards!
Words mean nothing
when you're dead.
Come on Junko!
Let's run!
Did she do that?
No way.
Not with a forty millimeter.
What are you guys waiting for!
Get the hell outta here!
Uh, what'd she say?
What are you
running away for girl?
It's not because of
that key you have is it?
I don't know what the hell
you're talking about you prick!
Key? Hey, Haru!
What Desert Pun--
Haru!
Desert Punk you bastard!
What did you do?
You must have really
pissed off the wrong person
to get Kong
breathing up your ass.
Look if you're involved
in some criminal behavior,
I'd rather just walk now
than get wrapped up
in this bloody mess.
You don't have anything
to worry about Punk.
This fight between me
and Captain Asstacular
is personal.
Damn. If I wasn't
in so much debt
I would just turn this job down.
And why do you have
to hang those things out
to dry in front of
my face all the time?
It blows my concentration.
What these?
I just can't stand wearing
this desert suit and helmet.
I figured I could do
without them in the morning
before it got too hot out here.
Liar! You're showing
them off on purpose!
Look at 'em, boing boing boing!
Oh God their so hot,
I wanna squeeze...
Oh no... Oh yeah.
You're a dead man
you scrod wrinkle!
You used us as decoys!
You're delirious!
If that was the case
I wouldn't be wasting time
trying to navigate her nipples.
I'd be running for my life!
By the way, he's not
trying to kill us.
What?
That's asinine!
We're all gonna die!
I don't think my dirty
shorts got that message DP!
I guess I have no choice.
Everybody! Keep your eyes shut!
Huh?
What the...
It's a heat-seeking missile
and an iron powdered smoke bomb!
All enemy tracking
devices are malfunctioning.
What is this...? It's blinding!
What are you doing?
Where are they?
I can't tell.
Wait! There they are!
Ah shit...!
There's a network of tunnels
at the bottom of
that dry well...
Don't let them get inside!
Uh, They went inside.
Damn jackass!
What the hell is that...?
A balloon?
I don't see anyone in the well.
I could be mistaken sir,
but I think I noticed that
Desert Punk guy in the group.
Looks like we've been had boys.
After them. To the east.
Yessir!
Phew. I thought
they'd never leave.
Next time you want
to bury me in sand
warn me first so
I can shoot you in the face.
There wasn't enough
time to warn you.
Plus it was our only option
for evading that tank.
Well I think it was
a stupid ass plan.
What would we have done
if Kong had decided
to stay and wait us out genius?
Beats me.
Geez. Why do you insist
on taking the
longest possible route?
Hovertanks have
trouble navigating
over such irregular
terrain dummy.
Whatever.
I wish you would have told us
we'd be going up against
the Fire Dragon Kong.
If I had told you that you
wouldn't have taken the job.
Yeah no kidding!
Oh man.
This has turned out to
be one craptastic morning.
Six million yen! Huh?
Well, if it isn't the
famous Machinegun Brothers.
And if it isn't Desert Punk.
What the hell
are you doing here?
Whatever you do don't
take off your helmet.
I don't want to
see your ugly mug
this early in the morning.
Ahh suck it.
Sorry to keep you boys waiting.
No worries. We just got here.
Huh?
Oh no. Don't tell me
she hired you guys.
W-Wait, you too?
That's right. We're a team now.
Let's have some fun!
Yeah!
Man. This sucks.
I really had no idea you guys
were childhood friends.
Hey, Akio.
Yeah.
I can't stop staring at those.
I know, I'd give anything
to have five minutes
alone with those fun bags.
So what was all
that crap earlier
about Fire Dragon Kong
not wanting to kill us.
What'd you pull that one out of?
I guess you weren't listening
to what that guy was saying huh?
Junko, isn't it about time
you told us everything?
You know about that
key you have lodged
between those enormously
beautiful breasts of yours.
Umm...
They want that key
but they're not willing
to kills us for it.
Why?
Because they run
the risk of blowing
it to smithereens along with us.
Now come on.
Spill the beans, baby.
What's the story on this key?
And why are they trying
so hard to get it?
And why don't you
take your shirt off
while you're at it?
Okay fine.
You remember this
from episode one, right?
I stole it after you
battled Pudding Boy.
This key actually belongs
to the wife of Taiko Okawa
who is president
of Okawa Industries.
The other day...
my family's armored
car was attacked...
The key to my late
wife's jewelry case
was in that car, and
was stolen in the process...
I'll make whoever
brings that key back
to me richer than
they can imagine.
That's what he said.
And so, it was his
eldest son Koichi
who hired me to
get it from Makoto.
Now, it's his second son
Koji coming for the key.
I knew right away this was going
to be worth lots of money.
I secretly contacted
the eldest son,
and negotiated
with the second son.
Man, I was pretty busy
for not actually
being in episode two.
So in other words
you were trying
to jack up the price.
Yeah that's right.
I sort of overdid it
and Koji came after me
with his precious Kong.
But here's the deal ,
as long as we can slip
out of Koji's area of the
desert without being caught,
we can make it to the East Oasis
where Koichi rules, and cash in.
Sound like a plan?
What? You babies not
up to the challenge?
Well, I uh...
We can handle it.
I'm sure there's
a way we can do it.
Ooh, uh, really?
Really? Great! What do we do?
How do we destroy
that damn tank?
Destroy? Are you nuts?
There's no way we
can destroy that thing.
We'll just run like hell.
You know, you're
plans kinda suck.
It's just like him.
Always thinking small.
Anyone who considers destroying
Fire Dragon Kong
as a viable option
is the biggest freakin
meathead in the Desert.
Huh?
Desert Punk?
Seriously, stop making fun
of him like that guys...
He's dead after all.
How can I not?
He was a major knob and
just a lousy human being.
There's nothing good to say.
He was also cocky
and had a potty mouth.
Let's be honest.
He was a useless, inept shrimp.
An all around bum.
Speaking ill of
the dead, are we...?
Even I find that
behavior despicable.
Look at you all.
You're nothing but
filthy animals...
And fools for turning
against me and my Dragon.
And because of that
you won't die easy.
Let's start with Miss jug-fest.
Get the key from that bitch.
It's my pleasure.
Boobies!
Huh...?!
Hiro just fell off
the damn cliff!
What the--?!
Dammit.
I'm gonna kill
you, you bastard!
Do you have any idea
how sore my body is?
I can't believe you're alive.
I can.
He's always been stubborn.
Even I thought it was the end.
Thanks to you all of
my precious possessions
have been destroyed
leaving me with nothing...
Like my zero-type helmet
I just had repaired...
My desert subsistence OS and
life continuum air module...
And the shotgun was a
keepsake from my father.
Shut it...! Put your hands up...
You're gonna pay
for what you did.
You stupid, ugly, smelly,
manipulative,
rich piece of evil...
I'll never forgive you!
Die!
What the hell are you doing?!
You little freak, get off of me!
I hate you!
Get your hands off of me!
Please let me shoot them sir.
Here goes!
I know what you're doing sicko!
No...! Give that back!
Give what back this
little key here...?
Come and get it!
Suckers!
No good. He's gone.
We're going after him. Mount up!
What's wrong?
The girl and the
others ran off too!
Damn.
That stupid Punk.
He really snapped back there.
This is not gonna be good.
What do you mean?
Whenever he gets like this,
there's no telling
what he'll do.
He could become so obsessed
with revenge that
he'd die and not care.
Seriously?
Hey we gotta do
whatever it takes
to get that key back
from Desert Punk!
Hell, I'll kill him
if I have to.
Oh the nerve.
He played us for fools!
Dumbass...!
He's got the key
on him, remember...?
We need it in one piece, damnit.
Hey, he's not
wearing his mask...
I'll throw some gas at him.
Oh no! Gas!
Great.
He's gonna get
squashed like a bug.
What a dumbass.
Left! Left!
No wait! Right! Right!
That was close!
He's bouncing around
like a damn flea!
I think I figured out
what he's trying to do.
What's that?
He keeps leading us
into wide chasms.
Keep coming baby.
So what? You think
he's leading us on?
I think he's gone
completely insane!
He's screwing with us.
If not for the key we would have
already ground him
into hamburger.
He's popping off that
pellet gun of his again!
Sir what should I do?
Crush him!
But the key!
I'd rather crush the key
than blow it to smithereens!
If it breaks then
we'll cut our losses!
Go!
Suck on this!
What's happening?
It's a cliff!
Idiots!
Eat me, you suckers!
Ouch!
Freeze!
What?
Pull your head out!
How many loose screws
do you have to have
to take on Fire Dragon
Kong like that?
Give me back the key, pipsqueak.
Y-Yeah, give it back.
And no funny business.
You guys blow.
Now quit interfering
with my business.
I'm having fun out there
and I don't want to be
disturbed anymore, got it?
If I can't get Kong,
I'll blow this key up with me.
You wouldn't.
If I hand the key over to them
they'll murder us
where we stand.
I'd rather take myself out than
kowtow to those bastards...
Or maybe I'll just...
Pull the pin right now.
Don't do anything stupid.
Yeah that guy... nuckin futs.
I told you.
And I wouldn't be
surprised if he did it.
You're right.
We know this because he's lobbed
grenades at us dozens
of times in the past.
I swear the guy's a mental case.
Awe. Isn't childhood
friendship beautiful...
Yeah, well I guess we
gotta go kill him now.
Evening Hiro.
Hey what's up?
You need a hand?
No!
I'm gonna get that
Desert Punk by myself.
And?
And... then I'll take
the key to Koichi.
So you're the
elder son's spy huh?
You could say that.
Are you talking about this key?
Yeah... Looks just like th...
Dammit! Where are
you Desert Punk?!
Sir!
There he is!
Get him!
I don't want anything
left of him once we're done!
You won't escape from
me this time Desert Punk.
Kill him!
That you Hiro?
Hiro...
Which way did you
see Desert Punk go?
What?
You are the first
and last person
to ever make a fool
out of me, Desert Punk!
Go to hell!
What the...
Look! It's Desert Punk!
He's going to let
that thing run over him!
What about my freakin' key?
No! There's nothing we can do!
I have to get it
from him! Let go!
I have one shot left.
The magazine's broken so
there are no second chances.
So Kong.
You're the biggest
and baddest force
in the entire desert.
No denying that.
And there's no way a guy like me
could defeat you, I'm small.
Oh, Shit.
I take that back.
You see losers,
your armor wasn't designed
to handle attacks from above.
That's quite a vulnerability.
This can't be happening to me...
It must really be you...
the Desert Punk...
Demon... of the Desert.
There goes the mightiest weapon
in the Kanto Desert.
There goes my key.
Yep, it looks like Desert
Punk was a idiot after all.
Look!
He made it!
He better have my key!
Hey, Machinegun Brothers!
Show 'em what you got!
Use that namesake of yours
and pump 'em full of lead!
Aim for the fuel tank!
Got it!
Abandon ship boys!
No way!
Yeah I don't want to get shot!
But if we stay
in here we'll get--
Fire Dragon Kong was too big
to chase a rat
down a narrow path
and its armor was too
thin in the worst place.
It only displayed its strength
in the wide open desert,
but here in the subterrane,
it was a sitting freakin' duck.
You've got snot
running down your nose.
Desert Punk and the
others finally managed
to get their hands on
the score of a lifetime.
The lesson for today;
Put a breast in front of him
and Desert Punk doesn't
know his ass from his face.
Which isn't really a lesson.
But maybe he'll
learn one, someday.
You're absolutely
amazing Desert Punk!
Do you realize
you're the first person
to ever defeat Fire Dragon Kong?
You sand-demon, you.
It was a piece of cake, baby!
Now let me grab on your--
Yeah, no.
It looks like the
only thing he's gonna
be grabbing is himself.
Start with one circle
Add one more circle
Then add one more big circle
Then a raincoat
blowing in the wind
It's actually a cape.
Whoa, don't forget
about the sunshade now
His heart is the
blackest in the desert.
His heart is black.
Shotgun is what he's gonna use
And then you've got
yourself a Sunabozu
He's on the run again
On the run again.
Just one more day and you'll see
He's got a job.
He won't stop
till tomorrow comes
He won't stop until
he gets the girl.
Until he gets the girl.
Get that girl!
Risking your life is
what you do, what you do
It's what you do
Yo! What's up?
I'm Desert Punk
and I want to say
that today was a
serious breast fest.
As for next time...
I'm Fuyo!
I'm Akio!
And I'm awesome!
No you're not!
Next time on Desert Punk,
"An Ace In The Sand!"
Don't miss it!