I am the one pushin' on ahead
just like you, yeah yeah
Won't you please hear me now
and give a name to
the demon in the desert
You can't help
but clench your teeth
As your heart starts
to tremble from the heat
Now stop it
It'll only bring destruction
Let's do it!
I killed an angel
The time has come
to stand and be strong
It's a sad history
hidden in a big story
That is the mystery
There's no way now of knowin'
Knowin' about what
tomorrow holds for me
So I just keep moving on
Living till the moment's gone
Forever just me
My mission
The great Kanto Desert.
Even in this wild
churning heat storm,
the few surviving souls
that make their home here
fall in love, it's their way
to validate their existence
by perpetuating the future.
But even then...
Procreation can
sometimes bring out
the worse in anyone,
causing even the normal ones
to be shunned by
others in society.
And no sooner, the right
punishment will always be
more than what
they ever suspected.
This is the reenactment,
front row seats
I might add, of ten days in
the life of a desert dweller
in this exact predicament.
Watch how fitting
the punishment is
for deviant behavior in
a harsh world such as this.
Now, my sweetie...
Say you don't mean me.
Faster woman! Use
those long legs of yours!
How about I use
them to kick your ass!
Come on, Master.
We don't need
the extra weight.
Why can't we just dump
the wench's body out here?
No way.
Im gonna use her till
she's dried up like a raisin.
Eww! Are you kidding me?
Listen up, Miss Sunshine.
Uh, yeah?
You head on back home.
I'm sure I'll be able
to quote-unquote "handle"
our fine traitorous
friend here myself.
What the hell
were those quotes for?
What are you gonna do to me?!
Fine... I'm going.
Finally, we're alone.
What's this about
you "handling" me?
If you're gonna take me
out, just man-up and kill me.
I'm not gonna kill you.
Then what it is?!
Round and round
and round you go,
and where you
stop no one knows!
Spinny, spinny, spinny, spin!
I just can't wait to cram it in!
Hello?
What is this place?
I call it Desert
Punk's Super-Secret,
Ultra Sticky Love Dungeon.
You've got to be kidding me!
Isn't it just the best?!
I ran across it
while scavenging out here
about five years ago.
These are all historic ruins
I found buried in the sand.
Course I had to
do some remodeling.
I haven't really
told anyone about it yet.
It might be corny,
but I kinda wanted you
to be the first
person to see it.
And here you are!
I'm honored.
Sorry about the
spinning and blindfolding,
but the exact coordinates
are privileged information.
I couldn't just
walk you on in here.
I have to say...
It's not such a
bad place to keep you.
Keep me?!
I'm outta here!
I gotta few things
to do, you know,
business, meet and greets.
There's food and
water in the back.
Just go ahead and
make yourself right at home.
Damn, I got a foxy hostage!
This just sucks.
That Punk...
He's certainly doing a fine
job of handling the traitor.
I guess I can't blame
him, though, I am pretty hot.
The tiny guy is alone.
I'll have plenty of
chances to bail on him.
I'll take it easy for a while.
Now, if I can just
find his hot tub.
But seriously he's
gotta have a bathroom.
I'm startin to smell funky.
The AC must be busted...
It's freakin' hot in here.
I'm gonna melt...
Can't take it...
He's waiting for me to die
from dehydration
or heat exhaustion.
Let me outta here!
Can anybody hear me?
Open this door.
Help!
This is for real.
I'm gonna cook to death in here.
Some body help me.
No... No way.
Perfume, brush,
towels, duckie...
A bath tub...!
Only rich people
actually have baths!
I've always wanted to
try one of these suckers out!
Oh... Who's gonna see me here?
Nobody's going to know.
This is the life!
I've never seen
such royal treatment!
If everyone could
have a dose of this,
I swear, there'd be
no problems in the world!
My skin's slick with soap it...
feels... so good.
I could so stay in this thing
for the rest of my life!
My clothes are gone!
Hello!
You, took them!
I didn't think you needed them
to enjoy my facilities here.
You turned off
the air conditioning!
Yes. I did.
I also ditched all of
those sweaty, worn out clothes.
There's nothing
sexy about dirt.
But I do have
replacements for you.
Don't say I never
gave you anything.
See, you tomorrow.
Not if I have any say about it.
Now he turns on the AC?!
The damn thing won't budge!
Where are my clothes!
I can't wear this.
I can't give that
perv what he wants!
I'm gonna catch pnemonia .
Fine.
I'll humiliate myself
and wear this damn thing
if you'd just stop
blasting cold air on me.
I gotta say, I
have good taste.
Women shouldn't wear
stinky desert uniforms.
They should wear bathing
suits and stripper heels.
That one-piece
makes you look like
six pounds of crap
in a two pound bag,
and those ruby
heels prop you up
like side of beef
in a window. Beautifull.
Why the hell did you
have me put this crap on.
You betrayed us.
You got in bed with the enemy,
and now you're my prisoner...
In the desert, the
sentence for your crime...
is hanging.
So, I can do
what I want with you.
I could chop you up...
No one would touch me.
It seems Junko's day
of reckoning has arrived.
Oh, yeah...
Your day of
reckoning has arrived.
Day of what?
I have a prediction...
About one year from now...
You will be
tending to a tiny baby
that just happens to look
a lot like the Desert Punk!
Yeah, all right.
I'll have your
stupid freakin' baby.
Well, okay...
I expected more
resistance from you...
being a strong, powerful
woman and all that crap.
I don't have any other choice.
I can go along with you,
or you can chop
me up, like you said...
I'd be stupid to
allow myself to get hurt.
Good, nice to know
your using reason.
What are your plans
after we have this baby?
I don't have any plans.
You're the one who's gonna
raise the little terror...
I can't get tied
down to my baby, mama.
I got my whole
life ahead of me.
Our purpose
really is to get it
on then knock you up,
not have some
ever-lasting relationship.
It's kinda my mission.
I feel obligated to
leave children behind.
Kids who will grow up
and take over
after I'm long dead.
Which is a ways off, so
lets get to the nitty-gritty.
Sounds good, champ.
I'm happy to raise the kid.
And I won't cause
you any trouble.
Yee-Haw!
You should scream...
Because one day
I am gonna have
this child find
you and neuter you.
My yam sack.
Ever stop to think
about your own offspring?
Desert Punk's kid?
It'll be maniacal,
hot-blooded, and born to kill.
A ruthless machine
of the desert.
The perfect
combination of traits
for someone who'd
snuff out his own father.
Gabba-goo.
It's me! Your daddy!
You recognize your
own daddy don't you?
Excellent! That was
just how we practiced it!
Good work, sweetie!
Gabba-goo.
You filthy skank!
Take my son and
turn him against me?
You're the one
who started this!
Just go ahead
and kill me then.
I don't wanna be apart of
your twisted game anymore!
The only thing that's
gonna get twisted is you!
I'll take that!
Good gracious crap.
I knew my junk would
get me into trouble someday.
It feels like they're
lodged in my throat.
You're the most
gullible kid I've ever met...
You actually thought
I'd let you knock me up.
I have standards.
What's the deal?
There's gotta be some
way to spring this door open.
I'm the only one who
knows the code for that door.
What is it?
That's confidential.
I know you can't escape.
You know you can't escape.
You know you can't escape,
and I know that
you now-- come to me.
Sounds confusing
but your only choice
is to become mine.
You got spirit. I like that.
Uh, Punk. You alive?
Please be faking!
I can't die in here!
You're the only one who knows
how to get us outta here!
I'm only gonna ask
you one time to wake up!
Wake up! Wake up!
You feeling better?
Yeah.
Then pop that lock
and let's both busta move.
Wait a sec... it's coming back.
But I forgot it.
How could you forget?!
Forget what?
Cut it out!
Where are we?
And who the hell are you?
Wait, who am I?
What's my name again?
I should've seen it coming.
A couple of smacks
to that small head
of his and now
he's got amnesia. Idiot.
Would you just
pull your head out of
your ass and remember?!
It's all coming back to me now.
That's great!
You and I were going
to do some babymaking.
Pass along genes...
perpetuate the future...
Enough, Don Juan.
This isn't the time or place.
You need to focus on how
you're gonna get me
outta this hell hole!
What did you say...?
The only one
hole I'm interested in
is the one you
have between your legs
that my kid's gonna
come marching out of
in about nine months or so.
You like that, don't you?
I never knew
that stripper heels
could be used so violently.
Based on my
observations, that's not
the only thing you
don't know about women...
Over time, we've learned
to use every accessory
we have as weapons.
Including birth control?
Well, I've always known
the best birth control
is simply to point at
it and laugh, little guy.
That mouth of yours could be
doing much more
than talking right now!
You ready for another round?!
Any of that jog your memory?
Type the damn code!
Uhh... I, uh...
What is it?!
I told myself to write down
the code but I didn't listen.
You let me know
which punch it is
that kick starts that
trashed out brain of yours!
I can't think when
your hitting me like that!
That doesn't sound
like a passcode!
Spit it out!
God. You're still hot!
I will beat you
all night until I get
the code out of
your sorry perverted face.
I'm gonna die in here,
locked in this metal dungeon.
I deserved a better way to go.
It's pathetic...
I have to die in a room
that smells like hot garbage.
You didn't have to you know?
You could have
just done what I wanted...
That way you'd have simply
walked out of here days ago.
Up yours...!
I hope you die first!
You know...
You get really nasty
when you don't get your way...
I bet daddy called
you princess all your life,
cause you actually believe it.
I hate you.
Hold that mirror
up to yourself, smart guy.
Every move you make
is to get yourself laid...
And the only
guys who act like that
are the guys who
have never gotten any.
That's a lie!
I've had some before!
I got some like...
uh, uh... Yeah...!
Three weeks ago, a waitress!
Yeah, she knew what it
meant to get "Punked" that day!
And that ain't no lie!
It's enouh to
make me wanna cry
when boys lie to women just
to make themselves look cool.
Yeah...? Does it make
you wanna cry as much
as those dumb-ass little poems
you write make me wanna puke?
My poems are good!
Uh, no, they're not.
I don't think I've
ever been this tired.
I know. I could sleep
for about a week.
We need some water...
And I already drained the tub.
Yeah, that was
all the water I had.
Did the air conditioning die?
I had to use up
all of the electricity
to get you
into that bathing suit.
I'm hungry!
Nothing like a tall glass
of orange water on a hot day!
Who the hell am I kidding?
I'm dejected and bored...
We have a job waiting
for us from Mugenya
and Master is
out there masterb--
You want one of these?
Totally, thanks.
Where's your boss?
Not that we really
care on anything.
It's not like
I'm scared of him.
He didn't hurt himself did he?
What do these guys want?
Thanks for the food guys!
Wow...! That's rich!
What is it?
What do you say?
Wanna go out with a bang?
Or maybe some heavy petting?
You just don't stop.
You're like an endless
stream of sexual angst.
Thanks, but I'm not
asking for compliments.
I think I have to
satisfy the temptation in front
of me cause I could
drop dead any minute,
and I want to feel
alive, just one last time.
That's not crazy, is it...?
I'm just a man.
You're right for
once... I'll do it.
You serious about that?
You're actually going
to let me touch you?
And you won't hit
me or nothing, really?
Right.
This is a dream come true!
But nothing freakish,
deviant, or weird.
Fair enough...
Let's get started.
Hold on.
No more holding me
prisoner or punishing me.
That ends right now.
We're gonna do this
on an even playing field.
One man, one woman.
Whatever you say.
I want it in writing.
Sure!
Thanks for this.
It's hard in
the world we live in
to be respected as independent.
And a thousand years from now,
when they dig up our bones,
you and I will
be seen as equals.
Which means a lot to me.
I can't thank you enough.
Even though I'll
try here very shortly.
I don't know why,
but just thinking about
doing you has worn me out.
Me, too.
I'm just...
I'm almost too tired to even
think about the next move.
We can catch a few
Z's before we start...
If that's cool...
Sleepy...
Oh, yeah, that's the stuff.
You're a dynamo!
Master, it's about
time you woke up.
Perpetuate my bloodline!
I have to make
baby while I'm still live!
Don't worry. I'm
doing it with Junko.
I signed a document saying
that we were both on the uh--
From the feel of things,
she and I already did it.
That's just gross.
Hold on...
Where the hell am I?
You're at the town
hospital in a bed.
Are we're here because
my baby's being born?
He says things like "Gabby-goo"
and I've already chosen
a name for the little tyke...
I'm gonna call him Punkie...
Will you cut
the moron routine?!
You sound like the "Punk"
in your name
turned into "Pathetic"!
What?
And now this whole
situation has turned to shit.
No, it can't be...
Was it a difficult birth?
I remember...!
Junko and I were
stashed away in my lair!
Wait one second!
How did you of all people
find my secret freakin hideout?!
A few months back
I saw you scurry off
into the desert with a
shovel and building supplies.
Naturally, I was curious.
You sneaky trick...
You followed me?
I did... And you
should thank me.
If I didn't follow you,
you'd be dead...
I had to find you
cause we got a
job offer from Mugenya...
But when I got to the hideout
the stupid door wouldn't open...
So I had to ask
the Machinegun Brothers
to use what they got
and bust into the place...
They did...
And we found you collapsed
on the floor next
to Junko the skank.
Where is she?!
What happened to her?!
You can't let that
filthy hose beast get away!
She left yesterday.
You let her go?!
I had to...!
She had a letter
signed by you that said
you absolved her of any
and all wrongdoings
in the past!
You had her
under your dirty thumb
for over a week
and then you just
let her slip away so easily.
Must eat you up inside.
She beat the
sense right out of me.
Akio check this out!
There's an assload of guns!
And look at all that ammunition!
This is a brand
new freakin bathtub!
Take it! Take it all!
I'm still hungry...
We can trade all this for food!
Oh dear!
Oh, this is wonderful!
Thank you! Thank you!
♪ Were going to
take whats yours. ♪
♪ Hey desert punk. ♪
♪ Were knocking
down your doors. ♪
Those bastard villagers
are gonna loot my place!
♪ Cause everybody's
procreating. ♪
♪ A sad life
we're sustaining. ♪
♪ In the desert. ♪
Master, chill the hell out!
♪ And we think
that you would too. ♪
♪ Ciao! ♪
Start with one circle
Add one more circle
Then add one more big circle
Then a raincoat
blowing in the wind
It's actually a cape.
Whoa, don't forget
about the sunshade now
His heart is the
blackest in the desert.
His heart is black.
Shotgun is what he's gonna use
And then you've got
yourself a Sunabozu
He's on the run again
On the run again.
Just one more day and you'll see
He's got a job.
He won't stop
till tomorrow comes
He won't stop until
he gets the girl.
Until he gets the girl.
Get that girl!
Risking your life is
what you do, what you do
It's what you do
Yo! Desert Punk here,
and I wanna let
you know that the, uh...
the Demon of, of something.
It's the, uh, the desert.
Those punches must've
really gotten to him.
Sorry. Anyway, the next episode
is called "A Change of Heart!"
I wonder what they're
gonna change it into?
My vote's for a load of cash!