Where am I? And why is
everything so white?
Junko, when'd you get out...?
Oh, right...
I'm dreaming. I know.
First, put your hand on my--
Welcome back... How you feelin'?
What the hell are
you doing here?
Look... I'm a nurse.
Can't you tell...
I got a clipboard.
I see the clipboard...
But the last time I saw you,
Oasis Intelligence guys
were hauling your
hot totties to prison.
How cute...!
You, were worried
about me, weren't you?!
Hey guess what Punk...
I lined up a new gig.
With the Underground
Mercenaries.
Your temperature is down,
but you still have
a nasty concussion.
You need to rest.
I'll check back
with you in a bit.
We'll run a few tests
and then maybe a bath.
Totally a dream...
There's no way that
chick would ever go
to work for an
organization of any kind.
Or this is my huge payoff
in the afterlife.
Yeah that's why she's here.
They ripped off all her clothes
and tortured her to death.
Stuck it to her
good in the showers.
She was wet and begging
for them to stop.
Now that gets the
gears turning. Down Charlie!
Kosuna?
What in the name of the
rose are you wearing?!
I know I look stupid,
but the googly
dingbat made me wear it.
Must feel weird to be
dressed like a girl for once!
No really, you look hot.
So, I haven't been
dreaming any of this?
Nope.
I think this place is like
Natsuko's hideout, or something.
I dunno. But the food rocks,
and I got to take a bath
for the first time this year.
We're actually
inside the West Oasis?
That's right.
But we're in some
totally obscure place,
way deeper underground than
the government even knows to go.
So I think we're pretty safe.
What's next for the two of us?
I wouldn't worry about it.
Just enjoy the down time...
And get some sleep.
You're no good
to me if you're rusty.
You're looking quite
at home, my friend.
It can't be! It's you!
Help! Help it burns!
My skin is melting off my bones!
What's his deal?
He always acts like that
around virtuous people.
You...! You can't be here...!
You're supposed to be
sold off, slavin' away!
I sold you to that
creepy hoof-sniffer back
at the human bazaar!!
Why do you have to suck so bad?!
Good to see you too.
How'd you get out of being sold
to that bald-headed percy pants?
I'll admit it was a bit rough,
but as it turned out...
Government forces
had been tracking me,
and they stole me
outta there pretty fast.
What a complete loser.
You couldn't even
save your own hide.
Whatever you say.
And I suppose you'll
say that I'm incompetent.
Ikeda... What the hell
are you doing back there?
I usually study Dark Ages
history for a living.
But last week...
they asked me to
keep an eye on you
and try to convince you
to join our cause ...
I evaluated your
character and found you
to be exactly what
we were looking for.
We know there's no
love lost between you
and the government.
You hate them.
Which makes you a perfect
candidate for conversion.
You should thank Ikeda for
bringing you into the fold.
I was just doing my duty.
Now that you know who we are,
you should know what we are...
We're the Underground
Mercenaries...
And we want to invite
you to join our cause.
What do you do?
We're clandestine
supporters of the future
and freedom of the
Great Kanto Desert.
We've put together a
group of mercs who stay
below the radar and work
endlessly for our cause...
And we are...
The Undergound!
AKA the Undergound Mercenaries.
The government doesn't
help those who need it.
They don't supply
decent food or shelter.
They won't even
keep people safe!
We have people both inside
and outside the
government's workings.
Together we can force change!
Please, Mr. Punk.
We need you on our side.
You're just the kind of guy
we've been missing on our team.
That's right...!
And you hate the
government like I do...
Who is a more perfect candidate?
We need your talents ...
The Underground
Mercenaries are just like you,
the only difference
is we're organized.
With your help, we can fight the
corrupt government bureaucracy
and make the
desert a better place!
What do you say Punk?
I dunno. I've always
kinda liked it.
The government isn't that bad.
Yeah, yeah, I got a short fuse
and they piss me off sometimes.
Same goes for women and
I ain't giving up on them.
I'm cool with the government
to a certain degree.
They manage the
farming, the medicine.
And it might only
be the bare necessities
that they're providing
to everyone to live on,
but that's life.
There're no easy roads
and no promises made
when you're born that
say your quality of life
is gonna be good.
They put it in your hands
whether you're gonna live
or die because in the end,
they don't really care.
I gotta say,
I kinda respect that.
So are we done here?
There's one person
you haven't heard from.
A major player in our movement.
Major player, huh?
The chairman of the Underground
Mercenaries... He's great.
You have a chairman?
It's me!
Caca.
Whoa... There's so
much tension here...
And all in one tiny room...
these two hotshots...
They really look like they might
hurt each other at some point.
This is like a battle of the
greatest!
The greediest man in
the desert staring down
the most driven treasure
hunter in the desert.
Kaizuka, the president of the
'Game of Living' corporation
with locked eyes on Desert Punk,
my master and total bad-dude
scavenger of the sands.
I see you brought your
runt-like friend along...
So what's with the
little school-girl outfit?
I'd rather be wearing sand.
Fill me in.
Why'd you snag Natsuko
and that moose-knuckle
Stryker to talk to me?
You already got this life
in the desert thing covered...
With your business and
all that disposable income...
I'd sit back and enjoy my life
selling stupid games
if I were you.
You're as cocky a bastard
as you've ever been, Punk.
My attitude is
just small time...
I can't hold a candle to
some guy who wanders the desert,
passing off old games
like they're gold,
manipulating innocent
people to do his bidding.
And dreaming of a
fairy-princess world
where everyone lives in
harmony with the government.
What a jerk.
As if you've kept
it in your pants
and never screwed
with innocent people.
He's got that crazy look again.
The truth of all this is that
I do have to discuss
a matter with you.
I made the choice to become
the underground's benefactor.
And I'll make sure that you'll
be earning plenty of money, too.
I figured it woulda
been a good ten years
before I got that call from you.
Things have become
more urgent of late,
and I think you know it.
There's a wicked force rising.
Something that will threaten
and take every life in
the desert if allowed.
You mean those
dudes from earlier
with the robes and the
hats and the pretty eyes.
Yes, I do. But not them alone...
You remember the
Guardian we ran into?
The power that
he carried with him?
Yeah, how could I forget?
Originally, the people like me
who came out into the
desert for excavation
were seeking items
from the Dark Ages.
But lately, it seems
that every piece
being dug up dates back to a
much more recent time period.
And the science
that courses through
them is dangerously high-tech.
High-tech?
What kind of high-tech?
Ah, your convoluted story's
beginning to make sense.
You've been scrambling
like a dog for table scraps,
desperate to get your hands
on one of those big bitches
to fight the government with.
You sure you're not
in this for the power?
Take over the government
and lead it yourself?
I can't lie.
That does sound nice.
Come on...
What are they talking
about that's taking so long?
Considering that
it's those two...
It's either boobs, world
domination, or boobs.
Why would Kaizuka
even be interested
in a shit-licker
like Desert Punk?
That's the kind of
question only a chick
who knows nothing
about Punk would ask.
Keep 'em up cutie.
During the Dark Ages,
catastrophic changes
affected the entire
planet, transforming
the Kanto Plains
into the Kanto Desert.
But mother nature
is a resilient lady.
The imbalances can be overcome,
and this planet will be
like it was a long time ago.
Sounds like you only want
things back to normal...
But, what is normal?
An environment where
things can live freely.
Take root in the
ground and grow.
Fruits, vegetables, forests.
Which all goes against
every government program.
Yeah, because they've
got this whole desert
engineered to benefit them.
Why would they
bother planting stuff?
Exactly.
The most recent studies
speak of a ten-thousand year
process to get our planet
back to her normal, green self.
Ohhh... 'Kay...
I'll be really dead by then.
So tell me about
your big plan, yea!
I'm not just in this
for the coup 'de tat.
Bringing down the government
is merely a single step
in the grand journey
I have planned.
This is about the greater good!
Restoring greenery
to this planet
with the help of my fellow man!
Greenery...
Yeah, that's a pretty dumb plan.
Let's get to it.
What do you need me for?
Underground Mercenaries.
Kick ass.
People are gonna totally
pay attention to me now--
We're big league now boys.
They made us a
part of their crew.
So, we've gotta be ultra cool.
We are so awesome.
You two check it out!
I even changed the banner!
Now everyone will know that I'm
an Underground Mercenary guy--
When did you do this?
Yeah, I didn't know
you could spell.
I always thought you
bought that banner.
Shut up. I can spell.
Rifle. R-I-F-U-L.
Now you try taintloaf!
You see something down there?
Yeah... But I don't
think it's down there.
That was good for me.
You done?
Yeah, and Kaizuka
said he was hungry.
Sure... I'll be
right back with it.
And...? Did you make the
decision to stay on with us?
Yeah. You're stuck with me.
You finally decided to
play for the good guys?
I figure if I refuse,
you kill me...
Or if I run, you kill me...
The choice to stay here
with you fine people isn't
much of a choice at all.
There's more to it, right?
I gotta make my money somehow.
Can you guarantee
you won't betray us?
You wouldn't believe me...
Not if it was yes... or a no.
You do have a point there.
We're counting on you...
Don't let us down Punk
Hey, there sunshine!
It's lunchtime! Yummy yummy!
A nice box lunch to eat up
and help you get better...
Here... Ahhh!
What's wrong?
Open up!
Oh...
Yeah... I know what helps...
He picked me up
like I was nothing.
I gotta keep him
from squashing me!
I got him.
Oh, crap.
Natsuko...
I have to tell... Natsuko...
Company.
I'll go say hi.
Holy ass nuggets...
Wait till you feast your eyes
on our sweet new gear...!
It's all light-weight
and everything!
Check this out! Rippin' cool!
Yeah!
You catch me,
and it's gonna cost you!!
Yeah...!
I'll just expense it to
the Underground Mercenaries!
I bet those guys
know what it's like
to go without a
piece for a long time!
Now, let's get these
horses outta the barn!
I hope I'm not
interrupting you two.
Yo, Tech! What's goin' down?
Not much.
Get that stalker away, from, me!
I'm not a stalker...
I'm part of the
Underground, Bitch.
Yeah, yeah. We're all friends.
Hooray...
Now, show me the goods.
Is that my new
suit you're holding?
Yes...
Identical in style
to your old ones
but fitted with all the
latest from the Unome suits...
I used their most recent
model... and I modified it some.
Your friends have
come back for seconds.
The dudes with the pretty eyes?
I think. You're
gonna get out there
and do something, aren't you?
It's not like I can say 'no'
and walk out the front door.
Welcome to the team.
I'll evacuate Kaizuka.
Junko, Tech.
Get your gear.
You're coming with me!
Right.
Ok, hold up. See you
on the other side, Punk.
Stryker, report back on
the evacuation status.
We're moving. No problems.
Get to the underground
parking lot and hold tight...
We'll meet you
there in ten minutes.
You're dead!
Get your indestructible
ass away from my sister!
Put them down...!
Don't hurt my brothers!
Haru! Stay back!
This is the coolest suit!
Kosuna...
Yeah-eh... huh?
As of right now...
My apprentice...
You're deemed
officially trained...
Congratulations...!
Starting this moment,
you are a
full-fledged mercenary!
Yea!!
That kicks ass! I'm the bomb!
Your first job is me leaving you
in charge of the
front of this place
while the enemy advances.
But... What about you?
Where are you gonna
dig in and defend?
Use your head, narwhal.
There's no way the attack is
gonna come from just the front.
This is a rebel base
with limited resources,
so they draw Natsuko
and the others out front.
All the while the real
target is in the back.
Where I'll be.
Be, careful out there.
Do you remember the last thing
Kaizuka said in the meeting?
Did you understand him?
The government won't
be removed overnight.
It will take some time.
And until everything
is complete,
I must continue
to run my company.
Keep up the image, you know.
But when everything
is said and done,
I'll make sure that
I pass it on to you.
Until that day, you must
continue to fight the fight.
What he meant was that
the shiz is gonna hit
the fan and splatter.
And we're the one's who get
to clean up the mudd afterwards.
I don't like any of this.
Stryker, Natsuko,
Underground Mercenaries.
It's a big, flaming
load in a paper sack.
What are you saying?
We don't take jobs to
fulfill some unselfish cause.
And we don't waste time
trying to fix something
that broke a thousand years ago.
We're mercenaries...
you and I... and
it's time to clock in.
Let's show them how
real mercenaries roll.
Yeah!
The front line's no
place for amateurs.
You're in charge
Mercenary Kosuna.
Mercenary me?
Do me proud!
Right on!
Mercenary Kosuna is
gonna rock the house!
It's a robot!
Natsuko!
Hurry! Everyone to the truck!
Escaping.
Get out of here, now!
We have visual confirmation.
That's Kaizuka!
He's their commander?! Amazing!
The president of the
'Game of Living' company
is running the rebel faction.
Ayuka you scored big time!
Get him in custody immediately!
Afirmative.
What...?! I'm going backwards!
Hold onto your pantyhose!
Kosuna!
Dizzy dizzy, round and round...
Restraints detected.
Movement is unavailable.
Thank you, Kosuna!
Enough gratitude!
Get me out from
under this thing!
Ayuka, update!
Do you have him yet?
Do you have Kaizuka?!
Negative. Negative.
Kosuna, you are
one bad little girl.
Yeah, nice job, short, stack.
Well, I am a real mercenary now.
What happened to Kanta?
He went the other way.
He said something
about showing you guys
what a real mercenary
was made of.
Coward.
You don't know anything!
He said the real attack
would come from behind!
And he went there all alone.
That's what a
real mercenary does!
He's no coward!
He did what you couldn't do...!
You don't know
anything about him!
Whoa, there really was
an attack in the back.
Freaky. I didn't expect that.
I was hoping they'd just follow
the barrage of people out
the front and leave me alone.
I guess the truth works
better than fiction sometimes.
No, does that mean ...
Kanta...
Ain't that just
the strangest thing...
Elimination of all
forces at the rear entrance
to the bunker is complete.
Forget the grunts back there!
Get to the front and
help Ayuka immediately!
Affirmative
Kosuna...
I can't...
I'm going back
and help my Master!
Get back here!
What are you doing?!
He needs my help! Lemme go!
Was he still inside?
No, Master!
Yo, this is Desert Punk,
I was killed today
and won't be returning.
Wait. Oh, come on
gimme my contract.
Where's my agent!
I need somebody to... Lawyer!
You were the
man Punk, the man.
Now that you're dead,
can I finally have
my porn collection back.
The next episode is
'Successor of the Desert'!