(light electronic music)
(bird crying)
(dramatic orchestral music)
(laughing)
(upbeat pop music)
(singing in foreign language)
- Darling!
Darling!
(clock chiming)
(alarm blaring)
- [Man] Come on, move it.
What's your problem, move it.
- [Man Over Loudspeaker]
This is an announcement
from the School Festival
Executive Committee.
Will representatives of
all classes and clubs
please come to laboratory
number three immediately.
- Pull!
Pull as hard as you can!
Put your backs into it!
- [Man Over Loudspeaker]
To the representatives
of all classes and clubs,
from the Festival Committee,
when using carts in the hallways,
please observe the speed limit.
Use of bicycles and
motorcycles is prohibited.
The school store will be open
during the School
Festival as Hama Teashop.
Today, we're having our
big Festival Eve Special!
Featuring Ramen Lite!
Less filling, but it's a whopping 30% off!
- [Woman Over Loudspeaker]
Between nine o'clock
and 11 o'clock, the Central
Staircase is only for going up.
- [Man Over Loudspeaker] To all students!
This is the Discipline Committee!
Wearing costumes before School
Festival Day is prohibited!
- [Kid] Hey, you!
In the Baltan suit!
Move it!
(screaming)
- [Man Over Loudspeaker] To all students,
from the Festival Committee,
will all girls please leave
the building by 10 o'clock.
Repeat, all girls please leave
- But do you really think anyone'll come
to a place that looks like this, Megane?
- [Chibi] Maybe we should have gone
for the Hot Babes Coffee Shop
like Ataru suggested.
Lum gave it her okay too, after all.
- I won't have Lum acting like a bimbo.
Besides, do you know how hard it was to
collect money from everyone
in class to open this place?
I'll be shot before I'll let it be
operated according to
Ataru's weird tastes.
- Weird tastes, he says.
- Speaking of whom, where's our fearless
leader goofing off now?
- [Chibi] Lum just went looking for him,
so he should be back soon.
- I swear.
- Hey, I'm sorry, but I gotta split soon.
I have to get the Hama Teashop ready
for the festival as well.
- [Mendou] Okay, thanks for your help.
- Oh, brother.
Looks like we'll be
staying here again tonight.
- [Chibi] We've got a real
manpower shortage here!
No wonder, considering
how unpopular Ataru is.
- Hey, you guys still goofing around?
When in eternity is your
shop gonna be ready, morons?
- So don't goof around, work!
Got it?
- What the?
- Hey!
We have tons of things to do
before tomorrow's opening!
So quit slacking off, and get--
(gasping)
Huh?
- Oh.
- Huh?
What's wrong with you?
(laughing)
Hey, isn't it a great idea?
If I go out looking like this, and really
toady up to the crowd?
We'll have a stampede of costumers.
(yelling)
- What's that?
Toadying up to the
crowd, looking like that?
Moroboshi, get out here now!
- Sir, could you avoid causing
any unnecessary shocks?
Even with the options
removed to make it lighter,
this Leopard still weighs about 40 tons
and I won't be held responsible for it
if it drops through the floor.
- What did you say?
Hey, Mendou!
I don't know if this
is an exhibit, or what.
but I didn't give any permission
to bring a tank in here!
- So you say, but there's
nothing to be done,
as it's already here.
Or maybe you would prefer
to just confiscate it?
- [All] Confiscate,
confiscate, confiscate!
- Shut up!