Defending God,
Queen and Country,
Our brave knights fell;
while in service to Sir Integra.
All praise to these
our fallen brothers.
This responsibility
rests squarely with you.
These men were
under your command.
For me there is no forgiveness.
This is all my fault.
Let us now consider
what personnel
we have still available to us.
Of the 192
personnel staffing the
London Head Office,
we have 57 that have survived.
Of those, 24 are wounded.
Mason Fox's unit of
25 men remain active,
having been dispatched
to Ireland earlier that day.
Eight other men who
were not at headquarters
are also ready for duty.
Why are Alucard and Seras
not included in this report?
Well, I imagine
listing them among the
dead would be redundant.
And what is
Ferguson's condition?
His lower jaw is broken.
It should take about
three weeks to heal,
But, he'll be fit
for duty in two days time.
Victoria here.
Mark the target.
I'll take care of it.
Get back!
Sir, the target
has been silenced.
Leave cleanup to
the district station
and proceed immediately
over to Hyde Park!
It seems like the
host is on the move.
We'll rendezvous with you there.
Right!
Hellsing's information
retrieval department
is now totally committed
to our investigation
of the Valentine brothers'
background and associates.
Through the round
table conference,
MI-5 has been asked to
assist in this research.
Maintain the investigation.
I want nothing overlooked.
This is...
Vengeance!
And they will pay
a thousand fold!
The Vatican's
special section thirteen,
It's from the
Iscariot organization!
To the most worthy
Sir Integra Wingates Hellsing,
as a prelude to the
approaching autumn season...
...a little outing to
the National Gallery is,
perhaps, in order?
Pardon me, so sorry
to keep you waiting.
Very well.
If you're too upset
for pleasantries.
Enrico Maxwell,
Head of the Vatican
special section thirteen;
the Iscariot organization.
To what do I owe the pleasure?
I'm here to offer my condolences
to you and your organization
135 dead in the line of duty,
and 24 injured, correct?
Rumor has it that a
rather brash Ghoul attack
has left your lot teetering
on the brink of collapse.
I've come today with my
sword sheathed, Sir Integra.
Oh shut up!
Your people have already
shattered the peace between us!
You sent Mr. Anderson
to attack us
and he has slain
one of my best men!
Don't pretend you've forgotten,
for we certainly haven't!
I will not indulge in this
ridiculous farce of civility.
Now get out of my country!
Or you'll what?
I offer you our kindness
but you insist that we be cruel!
So just shut up
and pay attention!
Father Ronaldo.
Recently, we've
had a bug infestation
spreading within Eternal Rome.
Through our laborious research,
we've concluded that these
bugs originate from England.
But because your sad little
club-house is in such disarray,
this infestation goes unchecked.
And your bug problem,
becomes our bug problem.
Make no mistake,
we have as little regard
for your Hellsing
Organization as we do
for the Vampire
filth we obliterate.
However, if you
insist on showing such
disrespect to the
Vatican's section thirteen,
We will not hesitate
to wipe you,
your organization and
your vampire problem
off the face of the earth.
Do you understand,
you squealing English sow?
English sow?
No wonder section thirteen
commands such respect.
What strong language!
To reign over the
kingdom of the world,
to make it's peace,
and write it's laws.
To be generous to the
obedient, and merciless
to all those who
would stand against you.
Nothing ever changes.
Two thousand years and you
still act like
the world is yours.
The Nosferatu... Alucard...
Damn monsters!
God it never ends!
Come in Victoria!
Report on our Target!
What's happening to the host?
Sir, the host has gone
underground into the tube,
attacked the passengers
and then escaped.
I've confirmed that
he's on the train
heading towards Queensgate,
but if the train
redirects at Notting Hill,
the situation's going to
be hard to contain, Sir.
Contact the main office, now!
Close every station
it's supposed
to pass on its main route.
Then order an emergency
stop for the train.
We've already dealt
with the Transit Authority.
Commence a thorough
sterilization of the premises.
Walter...
May god and Her Majesty
be with you, Amen!
What is it?
Please take a look at this.
This was taken an hour ago
at the Kensington Garden.
Code 00767!
ALERT the National Gallery!
Yes sir!
Pleasure to meet you,
Mr. Maxwell,
and now we should say Good bye.
What nerve. You dare
call my master a sow...
Really. I don't see how
I can let you leave here alive.
And now, O kings, be ye wise,
be admonished,
ye judges of the earth.
Serve the LORD with fear,
and to rejoice with trembling.
Kiss the Son,
lest he be angry...
...and ye perish in the way,
though his wrath
may quickly kindle.
Amen.
Captain Hook is moving to engage
Tiger Lily and the Lost Boys.
Maxwell! You didn't!!
Things being what they are,
you'd better hurry, Wendy.
This may be the
end for all of you.
Captain Hook
didn't come all the way
to London just
to kill Tiger Lily.
He'll be dealing with
the rest of London's
little lost boys and
fairy filth while he's at it.
Oh my god...
It can't be...
He'll dispatch
Tiger Lily and the others...
Then pay a surprise
visit on Peter Pan.
I see. Well then,
he's already here, isn't he?
Then Peter Pan should be
off to entertain his guest,
before he becomes upset.
The Vampire, and those
who ally with such filth,
all stand equal
in the eyes of God.
Sinful, dirty heathens,
to a man.
I act as God's own
wrath upon the earth;
raining down the divine
punishment of Heaven.
I will purify them all!
In the name of The Father,
The Son and the Holy Ghost...
Amen!
Fire!
Master!
How about a duel to the
death, Oh Judas Priest!
It's about time, Vampire!
What the...?!
I won't be killed
by anyone's lap dog.
Gotcha!
Master...
Master!
How pathetic.
Is This THING the best
that Hellsing had to offer?
I'd say that's a
little sad, really.
What am I going to do?
I...I mean...Master's gone and
all I have left is his...head?
What am I supposed
to do with it?
Dust to dust. Amen!
Master!
You foul monster!
I get that a lot.
But then, what's that make you?
A man?
A dog?
Or a monster?
And now you die.
You're fun!
Stop it! Why do you
have to be like that?
You Bastard!
Poor Vatican whipping boy!
I've had enough fun for tonight!
Oh, What? Are you going
to chew me to death?
Shut your hole you cheap
black magician of Hellsing!
I may not be able
to finish you today...
but next time...you die.
We'll meet again, vampire!
Master...Alucard...are
you all right?
He will never be
able to kill me.
That dog is neither
man nor monster--
Only a man can truly
hope to kill a monster.
Her Majesty's right honorable
Hellsing Organization will never
yield to anyone, grinding to
dust any obstacles in our way.
Should you wish to
live to see the morning,
run home quickly;
you degenerate...worthog.
What a beautiful day.
Young Miss, would you like
to go museum hopping with me?
Eh?
Then how about the library?
Huh?
You'll find secret treasure!
How dare you say that to me?
Such a difficult girl, right
Father Ronaldo?