I was told to give you this....
So tell me, why do you
want to be a vampire?
Well... because...
"All the Kingdoms of the World,
shall I give unto thee..."
You know, we get
a lot of riff-raff
trying to break into our scene.
Wanting to becomes vampires
so they can escape
their sad little lives.
I'm just...
The card is a ruse.
And any maggot
who dares to bring me
one of these cards is an
enemy of the Valentine Brothers.
No! It's not like that!
Britz told me about this place!
Go on...
Thank you for your patience
on this matter Alucard.
I believe you
will be very pleased.
Nice.
The 13mm Jackal;
a semi-automatic,
anti-freak weapon.
390mm long,
weighing in 16 Kilograms.
6 round magazines. Too much
gun for any human to handle.
Instead of the modified
rounds from your 454 Casul,
we've custom made an
explosive armor-piercing round
especially for this gun.
Hello...?
Casing?
Pure silver,
macadonium processed.
Ammunition?
NNA 9. Marbel cartridges.
Explosive or mercury charge?
Oh, Mercury, and of course,
they've already been blessed.
It's perfect, Walter.
I'm glad you're satisfied.
Do you think you could
you even kill the
Paladin Anderson,
with this gun?
Oh, I think so.
Miss Victoria,
very good. I have a new
weapon for you as well.
Oh, what is it?
The 30mm anti-freak
Harkonnen Cannon.
The Harkonnen Cannon,
uses two types of ammunition.
One, Depleted Uranium
shells; the other,
explosive armor
piercing incendiary rounds.
You're not seriously going to
make me carry
that thing, are you?
It really suits you,
police girl.
But, do you really think so?
I don't know if I would
look good carrying that.
I mean the length
is a serious issue.
But even that's
beside the point.
Isn't Depleted
Uranium is illegal?
And anyway, I'm a strong girl,
but I'm not that strong.
Your next mission
should be very interesting.
Miss Victoria.
I thought he was just
encroaching on our territory,
it turns out, this card was
the decoy from Britz' shop.
If Britz is the traitor,
why don't we just cap him?
Don't be so stupid Jann.
What?
The police arrested
Britz, last week.
He got busted?
Man, that's a mind-fuck.
Still, I don't think
a ordinary cop would
bring this card here and
risk his life so nonchalantly.
Any thoughts?
He was undercover.
Did he have a wire on him?
He didn't have anything
traceable on him.
Could be a sign; he may
have known what he was doing.
The only thing he
had on him was this....
It's from a special ops. group.
They claim to be
experts in dealing
with vampires and the ghouls.
Yeah, I saw them on TV.
Was'up with that shit?
It's high time
we stopped all these
territorial pissing
matches once and for all.
Don't you agree Jann?
Looks like we're gonna play
some war games, eah Bro?
But first, we're going
to need a few soldiers...
An MI-5 agent, who
was investigating these
artificial vampires,
has been found dead.
That is unconscionable.
When I was young, people
had some respect for MI-5.
No one would ever have
attempted such a brazen--
That's beside the point!
Madam.
Thanks to this incident,
forces all over England have
begun assessing what
sort of action is to be taken.
A round table conference
must be held, mustn't it?
I believe it must, and soon.
Hello? God, help me, please!
There's these vampires'
sucking everybody's blood!
It's true!
I'm not fucking around!
It's true.
I'm not fucking around.
It's time for us to leave.
Step it up!
You demonic vampire bitches!
Forget this.
According to reports
by the local police,
Those people being attacked were
some sort of religious cult.
Reconnaissance says they
may have illegal weapons.
No need to be
beat about the bush.
Ghouls or not we're
going to be dealing with
some especially
dangerous scum tonight.
Humbly accept your orders,
and May God and
Her Majesty be with you.
Amen.
Shouldn't I be going with them?
I want the human
troops to handle this first.
You're just going to have
let them take
care of it, Alucard.
Humans are always so willing to
tangle themselves up
in meaningless rules.
Besides, the new gun Walter
got me, begs for a field test.
Alucard, the target
they are about to fight
is not just another
inhuman freak.
These vampires have
human characteristics
that may be difficult for a
creature like you to comprehend.
That sounds like a
good to be a lot of fun.
Target Acquired.
Confirmed as NHB!
Fire!
What is this?
There are no targets on scene.
We don't even see any bodies.
Blood. I smell blood.
But' it's not just blood!
All this for just one vampire.
Get out!
I won't let our men die,
not because of me.
It took us too long to
recognize the booby-trap.
We still managed to evacuate
everyone. I'm very sorry ma'am.
How dare they underestimate
my organization!
That freaks!!
Come in
Sir Integra.
The knights have arrived and
are ready for the conference.
It's rare these days for the
Knights of the Round Table
to wear their swords.
Sir Integral Wingates Hellsing,
the knights of the
modern world have more
effective weapons that swords.
Now, kindly take your seat.
I doubt any of us
has much time to waste.
Sir Integra, according to your
report, many of the creatures
you have been encountering
recently are man-made vampires,
due to these implanted
freak-chip devices.
The mission of the
Hellsing organization is to end
all earthly activity
of non human creatures.
In the process of completing
this mission, we are expected to
have many direct encounters
and battles with vampires.
But it is not our
responsibility to investigate
the mechanism of this chip,
or to determine
who is distributing it.
We are in the midst of
conducting our investigation.
And investigation during which
you let the enemy kill your spy.
They even stuck a
Union Jack in him.
You misunderstand your
situation, Sir Integra.
We all attended the
round table conference
to share our power and
knowledge with each other;
out of loyalty and
reverence to her Majesty.
I understand.
No, Sir Integra.
I don't think you understand.
You see, your activities have
become a bit too flash of late.
Non-human creatures have
existed since ancient times,
and Great Britain has
managed to keep this quiet,
controlled, and contained,
up until recently.
Your Hellsing organizations
current activities
are leaving a stain on
our illustrious history.
Hellsing has been
too loud, and too public.
One could wonder if your
qualified for your job.
The enemy is armed with powerful
weapons. I have had no choice.
As for Information control...
I believe that's your job.
That's beside the point!
There is a limit to how much
information can be suppressed!
So you are telling me that the
round table conference members
are not powerful enough
to handle the situation.
You're overstepping
yourself, Integra!
Your father would
have never been so
irresponsibly brash!
My father; was my father.
So, you won't believe
what he did next man.
It's too fucked up... After he
ran Soho's bar out of business,
he fucking poached all the
girls from his place, man.
So like, Soho totally
fucking snaps...
Oh do, shut up.
Bro, what's wrong
with you, man? Hey!
You always get so
annoying before work.
I've said it before; I know
I'll probably say it again.
Please learn to work quietly!
Yeah, yeah. I've heard
all that before. I know.
Christ!
You have no excuse
to screw this up, Jann.
Screw Up? That's
never gonna happen bro!
This shits gonna be a cake walk.
Excuse me! Sorry Sir,
this building is off limits.
I am gonna have
to ask you to leave.
Oh, I'm sorry.. We're here
on a sight seeing tour.
We're taking a tour of
all the old London mansions,
seeing some famous
castles in the countryside.
This one is our first stop.
What're you talking about?
This place is...
Isn't this place supposed
to be open to the public?
I know all the people on
our tour bus over there
have just been dying
to take a look inside.
This is main entrance,
I have some suspicious
persons here. Please send-
Oh, Jann. I think it's
time to start the tour.
What's wrong?
Give me a status report!
Jesus Christ! You suck!
You all fuckin' suck!
As long as I can keep
killing and keep drinking,
whatever works is cool.
Killing Hellsing,
Killing whatever. Fuckin' man!
I'll just kill' em all!
Integra!
What's happened?
What's going on?
We are under attack!
It seems to be an unknown
number of enemy ghouls,
all fully armed.
They're disorganized,
so I'm having trouble
predicting their movements.
They have already broken
into the compound
in several key points.
I am so fucking hard right now!
We are smarter than you
bitches, and you can't stop us!
It's a disaster.
Integra! Sir Integra!
Good lord. They're attacking
the Hellsing house,
I can't believe it!
What is all this about Integra?
Explain yourself!
Integra!
All outside units
report back immediately!
We must defend the
third floor at all costs!
My God, they're
already this far.
You know, the security in
this place is so fuckin' weak!
What to do?
Old peoples' blood
taste like a shit.
But, it's no fucking
fun if I just shoot you...
Ferguson! Come in!
Ferguson!
Bastards!
I'm Janny.
Excuse me.
And I'm Luke.
Hey...
With the weather report.
Hangon...
Next week, Hellsing
will have a rain of blood.
Again, being silly...