Amen!
We'll move in before dusk.
I do wish we had
more intelligence
on this Boobhan Castle.
Can't be helped
Assess the situation
inside quickly.
Subdue the freaks!
Understood.
Walter.
Sir Integra,
as per your inquiry,
Boobhan castle is the
property of a Japanese firm,
but it's currently
up for auction.
This castle seems
to be the ideal
home for a mock-vampire.
Running with this
thing is such a bother.
Stand ready!
It's wrong.
Victoria, what was
that you just said?
There's something here...
Yes, sir.
Roger.
We're pulling out!
Why is the SAS here?
I am hereby ordering
your organization
to make a complete withdrawal.
This tainted castle must first
be purified by the
Hellsing organization.
Well, the situation has changed.
We've discovered
that the IRA have been
using this castle
as a weapons depot.
There is a high possibility
that some of the most
wanted terrorists in this
country are still hiding inside.
Even if they have
become something inhuman,
that doesn't mean their guilt
as terrorists has
suddenly been erased.
We already know about all
your gear and your strategies.
Just try and remember
you're not the only
outfit trying to
protect this country.
Packing up then?
I will be filing a
complaint with the JIC.
Withdraw!
Your intuition is
getting sharp, police girl.
Master.
Police girl.
The battle we are
joining now is unlike
anything you've
ever seen before.
Prepare yourself.
It almost sounds like
you're enjoying this, Master.
Oh, but I am!
Welcome home, Sir Integra.
Young Laura has
been waiting for you.
Laura?
Laura Hellsing...
Integra, it's been too long.
Laura...Hello dear sister.
You should have called ahead.
Though it's good
to know you still
haven't mastered
basic etiquette.
All of the family living
in Avon are doing well.
That's good.
Don't you ever get
lonely living here, Integra?
Why don't you stay here tonight?
I'll have Walter
prepare a room for you.
Thank you, sister.
There's no way I can
sleep before taking a bath.
What's... that?
Miss police girl?
God, don't scare me
like that! I mean...
I know I may not
be human anymore,
but nobody no
matter what they are
likes to be
frightened like that!
Christ!
My apologies for startling you.
So who is that girl?
That would be Miss Laura.
She is Sir Integra's
younger sister.
Her sister?
But they don't even look alike.
Well, I guess their family
does have a complex history...
...so I suppose things
like that could happen.
Walter...?!
Excuse me.
I sometimes forget I not
as young as I used to be.
I believe I must take
my leave for the night.
Have a good evening.
Something's...not right.
How do you manage to get
lost in a castle this small?
Reminds me of a
ghost story I read once.
Near the end of World War 2,
the Nazi's invaded Transylvania.
They were stationed
at an old castle,
and there was a
demon in there with them.
Hey, are you listening?
Your Name?
Paul...Paul Wilson...
Do you want to live?
To live...of course...I...
Do you want to live forever?
Forever...I don't know...
Do you want to stay
in the form of a man,
broken and imperfect?
Imperfect?
Or do you not want to
become a perfected being?
I want to be perfected...
that's why I've
been training myself.
I even joined the SAS,
although it hasn't
been working out.
Do you want to live forever?
I want to live... forever.
What are you doing here?
Has your hunger
driven you to this?
I don't know your name yet,
but I think we have
a lot in common.
You've also put aside your pride
and learned to bow
before human masters.
How utterly...pitiful.
What are you... doing?
Laura...
Walter! Sir Integra is...!
Don't you dare try
to disturb Sir Integra!
God damn it! I... oh god...
I don't have a sister!
I've never had a sister!
I knew something was wrong.
You evil bitch!
How dare you do this to me!
I do hope you have
some power to back
your enormous pretension?
You're Alucard.
What shall I call you?
I'm Incognito!
So you're nobody?
I can live with that.
My name's a bit
of an Enigma as well.
We're both originals
who were bound by humans.
Let's take our time
and have some fun.
Laura...is your using that
name part of some sick joke?
Is it?
There was a Laura who was
taken by the Countess Karnstein.
Tell me your true name
Buvanshee. Are you Carmilla?
Did my ancestors in the Hellsing
family destroy your people?
Is that it?
You really came here
for your petty revenge?
I wouldn't bother to
waste my soldiers time
sorting out a sad
she freak such as you.
Your nothing but a...
Stop it Walter! Please wake up!
Please!
You have such a
dirty mouth, big sister.
What are you
waiting for, Incognito?
Don't you carry
any human weapons?
An Armscore
40mm MGL, how quaint!
I wonder what kind
of projectiles it fires?
Explosive rounds?
Sorcery from the Dark Continent?
Perfect. Let's begin.
The two of us. We're different.
What did you say?
The difference between us...
Is you don't have
a master, anymore.
Alucard...
What have you done!
Walter please...
I'm going to fill your flesh
with my Jackal's bullets...
Your blood is
delicious sister...
Do you think
you're torturing me?
On no, I'm only doing
what I was told to.
They told me that I shouldn't
make you into a
ghoul too quickly.
But I think it's just about
time to take care of that.
Now dear sister, I am going
to chew my way
through your neck,
and drink up every last drop
of blood until your dry.
Your delicious blood...
Then I will give you just
a little bit of my blood.
Just a taste though, since
I can't make you one of us.
You will become nothing
but a mindless ghoul.
So sorry.
What was I doing?
God...
I've had enough of
your mockery, Buvanshee!
Stay Back!
Sir Integra!!!
There is impure
blood in my veins!
I'm the fairy that lives inside
your Hallconnen cannon
Oh?
Actually the trigger is in here.
Do you wish to test
my Hallconnen cannon?
I'm not touching that.
Wait! It's very strong.