Five Three Zero Zero, Roger.
Arial units stand by until
ground troops arrive. Over.
Target is confirmed.
Releasing control art
restriction system
to level three.
Please come in.
Perhaps you would
care for another drink?
Your beauty makes me want
to drop down to my
knees, caress your legs,
and prove how much
I admire beauty such as yours.
But that sort of game is
reserved for younger gentlemen.
Still, I feel very fortunate to
have met you at that party.
I just know that you're
the kind of person
who will truly appreciate
my strange, new appetites.
Do you mind? I find
the dark more liberating.
And your beauty
lights up the night.
You smell delicious...
Who's that?
What are you doing here?
Situation C. Keeping
power restriction unlocked
until the target
has been silenced.
What are you doing in my home!?
Who do you think you are!?
The Hellsing Organization.
What do you mean?
No, wait! Please wait!
Out of the way, human!
Unless you'd rather become
a miserable little Ghoul!
Vam...pi...re...
Limited release completed.
On 12 June, this priest
was assigned to a small church
in the Village of Cheddar.
One month later, the first wave
of missing persons reports
began flooding in.
The local police
conducted the investigation.
The day before yesterday,
officers were sent to the church
to apprehend the suspect.
All of them were
reported killed.
It was then that the
London Police Authority
ordered D11 into action.
Yesterday,
special Division 11 sent
in one unit of
their elite troops.
Fifty percent
casualties were suffered.
What's worse, it seems
our men were killed
by the officers reported
killed the day before.
They're no longer human.
What?
These people have
had their blood drained
to feed the vampire.
They've become
cannibalistic Ghouls.
You have taken the lecture.
Well, I didn't know they
weren't human anymore!
Lieutenant, it is
not my responsibility
nor my intention to
dwell on your mistakes.
What are you implying?
You're a lieutenant in the
London Police Authority.
That would lead one
to assume you possessed
the knowledge
and intelligence to
accurately assess the
situation in Cheddar.
And that you would
know the correct response
in these situations.
But somehow, you forgot,
there is only one way to
resolve these problems.
I imagine you
were quite prepared
for these sorts of consequences.
But it wasn't like that.
I didn't forget about
the proper protocol,
the Hellsing organization.
It's getting dark...
Sir Integra Hellsing...
My organization has already sent
assistance to Cheddar Village.
How many agents?
One.
One?
What a perfect night...
The kind of night that makes me
want to have a bite to drink.
Seres...
Try not to talk Jack,
Reinforcement's
will be here soon.
I just wasn't
ready for this. I...
I Just can't...
It's too much.
I'm trying to be strong.
I don't want to be nicknamed
kitten for the rest of my life.
I'm sorry...
I swore I'd never cry
at a crime scene, Jack.
Jack!!
Please don't make
me do this Jack...
Sorry!
Your O.K.
But you can't be O.K.
You guys are all dead!
Andy! Eugene! Hey!
Don't you recognize me?
It's me Kitten!
I'm letting you know
that I'm already
on my way to Cheddar Village.
Please try not to worry,
the Hunter I sent in
is perfectly suited to
this type of situation.
Just leave everything to us.
This...this is not the sort
of thing...I expected...
when I signed up...with D11.
A monster...
It's not human...
Beautiful night,
isn't it, police girl?
It's especially beautiful of
course, if your a blood sucker.
You're not human...
Why, would you have
shot me if I was?
What on earth am I doing?
I don't know anywhere to
go that's safe around here...
The church has
always offered sanctuary
to those who are in distress.
Good evening Father...
And a very good evening
to you young lady,
so fresh, so full of life.
So frightened by the evil
creatures that walk the night,
Poor Little thing.
Are you really a priest...?
I am merely a guide,
to the weak of heart.
Well, I'm on a mission.
We were supposed to
deal with this priest who...
But, you're not like
the rest of them...
You're speaking of the
Ghouls that you saw outside.
Ghouls?
They are the undead
slaves of the vampire.
When a vampire
drinks a humans blood,
the corpse left behind will move
under the vampire's control.
Vampire?
Of course, vampires
can't turn every human
they drink of into
one of their own.
For example...
Let me go...
Changing you into a ghoul
would be such a waste.
The blood that
courses through your body
is warmer and sweeter
than you can imagine...
Let me go... or else...
I'm... going to shoot...
and I'll blow
your brains out...
and then everyone
will find out...
I know you're feeling pain.
But I will give you pleasure.
And it will last forever.
I had enough of you...
God damn punk!
And who are you?
My name is Alucard.
I am but a servant of
the Hellsing organization.
I deal with garbage like you.
Garbage like me?
Who do think your talking to?
Have you lost your mind?
No, you're even less than
garbage...you're just scum.
And that ridiculous costume...
You look like some sort
of sad carnival freak.
Just look at you wearing
those priest robes.
Don't you have any shame?
I thought scum could
at least feel shame.
I think you should die now.
Captain...
You are a fool who creates
slaves to do his dirty work.
A coward, and an incompetent,
incapable of doing
anything on your own.
You're not worthy of
the lowest pits of hell!
Just kill him!
It looks like
somebody was all talk.
What?
Oh God...
Shooting me is not
going to do you any good.
One of us...
You'll need more
than guns to stop me.
Hurry up and kill him!
He's not human...
Stop it! What are you doing?
Both of us are vampires!
You act more like a cockroach
than a proper Vampire.
Left on your own you would
cover the world in filth.
I can't stand your kind.
You don't have the self respect
to be a vampire,
you undead maggot.
You barely know what you are!
As for me. I have my own reasons
for serving my human master.
But that's not a story
for trash like you.
This fires a 13mm
explosive round.
A silver cross from
Lanchester church
was melted into the
alloy for the bullets.
Prepare yourself for
an eternity in hell!
You'll have to kill
the girl to get to me,
and I don't think you can,
play thing of the humans!
But come now, we're
both vampires, no?
Humans are less than
cattle compare to us!
Forget your human
masters, let me escape!
You could even come with me!
We could work together...
Can't you understand.
We could be powerful together.
Two vampires.
Two strong vampires!
Police girl.
Yes...
Stop it! Are you
listening to me?!
I'm going to fire my gun now,
and the bullet will
rip through your lungs
before it hits the
maggot vampire's heart.
I...but...wait a minute!
I know you don't
want to die tonight.
Do you wanna come with me?
No, now hold on...
I can't force you into this.
The decision has to be
made of your own free will.
So make the choice!
Yes.
Alucard...
Remember that the choice was
always yours, Police girl.
This is where you're
supposed to close your eyes.
Mission objective accomplished.
The target vampire
has been silenced.
The Limited power
release is completed.
It took you far too long
to silence just one target.
I'll have someone
take care of her.
No.
I want you to
transfer the police girl
to the Hellsing organization.
You don't make decisions.
The police girl made
the choice for herself.
It's time for us to leave.
Um...
This was a perfect
night... Right?
No chicks, no romance, no sex.
Who says chicks anymore?
Who are you anyway?