You just don't
know when to quit...
You've run out of your
puny man-made bullets,
blessed with the
power of your puny God.
Clever bastard...
Master!
Police girl.
Master! Quickly!
Run away! Now!
Not like this.
I can reach it...
Please not like this...
This cursed tower
cries out in hunger,
eager to consume your blood.
This tower is an
old and decrepit ruin,
it suits you perfectly.
Master...
I'll send you to the
deepest pits of hell!
And while you're there
you can lick the
devil's ass, Incognito!
How does it feel Alucard,
to have a taste of your
own blessed silver bullets.
Master!!!
Go faster.
I promise we'll be
there soon, Sir Integra.
Attention Hellsing Organization!
Turn around immediately
and follow our instructions!
Do not...
I wish we had
equipped the helicopter
with sidewinder missiles.
We'll talk about it at
the next budget meeting.
Master...
Police girl...I
am your master...
you should have listened to me.
Seras...
Don't do that...
Alucard, my master...
Even if you lick every last drop
of your master off the tower,
you will never be able
to become a true Nosferatu.
You bastard!
You're loosing a lot of blood,
and soon you will run out.
You're already dead and there's
nothing for you to
be afraid of anymore.
Run from this place,
Seras Victoria!
That's enough Walter.
I don't want to
risk losing you next.
Orders given by the Hellsing
Organization must be executed
even at the cost of our
own lives, Sir Integra.
Please try and
endure the situation
for just a while longer.
Walter...
Walter!
Roan Veldai Shukuku
Nebreften Zarzas Zarzas Nerzas!
Oh, it's you.
Agun Dem Dortem Wieden Lar!
What are you trying to conjure?
Are you trying to summon
something from hell?
Rott Gar! Sett!
My God, it's Sett...
You're not really
bringing that demon here?
I will destroy everything!
I was born to bring
ruin to all that is.
Do you really think
I will allow myself
to be a part of your
filthy demonic magic?
Sett will enter me,
and together we shall
send this cursed town
crashing down to hell.
And you, my young Hellsing.
You will make my power strong!
You are nothing but
a freakish blood addict
who will soon enjoying
an eternity of pain!
How marvelous you are!
I'm going to violate
every part of your being.
I will consume every last
part of your body and soul.
Leaving you in ruin...
Situation A!
Unlock limited release
control system to level one.
Activate the
Cromwell initiative!
Your master
Hellsing commands it!
Your servant has long
since been destroyed.
Now it is time for
you to know your death.
I want you to scream!
I can taste your sweet blood
rushing through your body.
Acknowledge my
approval! Alucard!
Alucard!
Limited release
approval is confirmed!
Releasing control art
restriction system to level one!
My Master...
Yet another
beautiful moonlit night.
He's not human...
It's you...
I have feasted on the
untold rivers of blood
that has soaked into
this cursed fortress.
The Bloody Tower has revived me.
Now, what technique
shall I use to send you
to a purgatory of
eternal pain and torment?
Sett, God of Chaos,
who dwells within me!
Consume this vampire
in the flames of hell!
That's the way of
true A-list vampire!
At last I've found a
suitable creature to battle!
Alucard! The true
immortal vampire!
Is this all you've got?
Even after you awaken
that dried up hell demon
and take him into your body?
Is this really all
the power you can muster?
I will see you grovel
before me in disgrace!
You will become part of me
and serve Sett for eternity.
Master...
Where is Alucard?
He's winning.
No matter what, he'll win.
My Master.
It seems that your were not
just another simple braggart.
But no matter,
you cannot destroy me,
For I am imbued with the
power of the most ancient god.
I welcome eternal pain!
You have such disgusting tastes!
Is pain truly your pleasure?
Then I will grant your wish.
I'll send you to a world
where all you will know is pain!
But don't let
my fun end too quickly!
Come on! What are
you going to do?
Come on! Show me!
Hurry! Hurry up! Hurry!!
The world began before
the vampire Alucard existed.
And it would do for the world
to see you die before it ends.
Now, disappear forever, Alucard!
Are you really trying
to shoot with a broken gun?
No, it's not! It can't be!
Impossible. Who are you?
Integra, my master!
Your orders...
The decision is yours.