I'm sorry.
If only I had gotten there
just a little sooner...
You must pay close attention.
Watch how Integra
fares in battle.
Battle?
Integra tore
through her own throat.
She shed her own blood
and chose to fight for her life.
Giving in is what kills people.
When you refuse to
surrender with all your heart,
only then do you
transcend your humanity.
Even in the face of
death, never give up.
That is the strength
of our Master.
Master...
Blood pressure?
Steady at 100.
Right, let's get started then.
Scalpel.
Yes sir.
Intelligence reports
that Boobhan castle
has been destroyed.
However, Sir Islands...
We...No Sir. We still
have not heard from any of the
66 members of the
SAS 211th division.
Hemostat.
All right, we're in.
Excellent. Beginning
arterial anastomosis.
Tweezer.
Oh god, I'm running late.
Morning Father.
You're five minutes
late, Integra.
Well, why don't we
start today's lesson.
Ready?
Yes, Sir.
Now Integra,
what creature is
dreaded above all others?
It's the Vampire.
Correct.
And just why is the
vampire so fearsome?
Once the sun has risen,
they may only find rest
in a small, dark coffin.
Nevertheless, vampires are
considered nearly unbeatable.
Now why is that?
They feed on human
blood. Create ghouls,
and increase their
brood without limit.
An absolutely
terrifying creature,
yet it's not totally unbeatable.
Um, they won't die
unless you stab them
with a wooden stake?
Do not be fooled by old stories.
Their defeat does not
lie in such simple tricks.
Is their power truly that great?
Yes, they have
powers that let them
tear through men like rags.
They are cunning and smart,
and operate with their own
unknowable inhuman logic.
That is the vampire.
Do you understand Integra?
The vampire is an intelligent,
blood drinking demon.
The task appointed to our
family is to protect the Queen,
Great Britain and
the Church of England
from machinations of
these fearful creatures.
We are called upon
to be a holy shield and,
sometimes, a righteous sword.
We have inherited this honor
from the many noble knights
and secret sects
that have preceded us,
and we gladly accept
this sacred office.
I understand.
My hour has come, Integra.
My will is that you and you
alone will lead the family.
I call upon you to be the
next head of our sacred order.
Father...
Richard, my brother, be a guide
and support to my daughter.
Of course, brother.
Integra, there is so much I want
to tell you if only
I had more time...
The honorable blood
of the Hellsing family
flows through you.
Yes.
Remember, Integra, be glorious.
Blood pressure
has dropped to 75.
All right.
Lets deal with the blood flow.
Suction.
Father...
Master of my master...
That's the most ridiculous
thing I've ever heard!
It's unprecedented Sir,
but this plan already has
the Queen's personal approval.
God Damn it!
There's only three days left
until the succession ceremony.
I have waited 20 years
for my brothers' demise.
I will not have the
organization stolen
from me by that brat!
So why haven't you
found Integra yet?
Do you realize
Walter will return
from South America tomorrow?
Do you realize how difficult
his presence will make this?
But we've checked the
building top to bottom, Sir.
No more excuses.
I want this to end tonight!
The sub levels have
yet to be searched, Sir.
But those sub levels
have already been
sealed off for well
over 20 years, Sir.
In my opinion, she's already
made good her escape.
The sub levels...
Black arts room,
eugenics laboratory,
interrogation room,
autopsy theater, dungeon...
I can think of no
more fitting a place
for trapping filthy vermin.
The brat is hiding
somewhere in the sub levels.
Kill her on sight.
We can forge our excuses later.
Now go!
It's only been three
days since father died...
Bastard! Do you have
any human soul left in you?
If you should ever be
confronted with a true crisis,
where all hope is lost...
Make your way to the
forgotten underground prison.
There, in one of the cells,
lies your protection.
There you will
find the consummation
of our Hellsing family's
greatest achievement.
You've given us
quite a chase, Integra!
I'm sure you don't really need
to hear the full
explanation for this.
But for the future of
my country, my church,
my Queen, and
my sacred Hellsing family...
...you will die.
Uncle...what kind
of man are you?
Can't you understand?
My father entrusted
Hellsing's future to me
because he feared you
would be reduced to this?
You...damn brat!
Do you think I won't be willing
to shoot a little girl,
well, do you Integra?
After all, both of
us are Hellsing's...
I know you don't
want to die tonight.
Stitching up the wound.
We'll just have to wait and see.
Walter?
Miss Victoria, I wish
to apologize for last night.
Despite the dark magic,
it was unconscionable.
I hope you can forgive me.
Please, there's no
need to go on like that.
I'm all right.
But, what's this?
Sir Integra will
want her afternoon tea.
Today's blend comes from
Ceylon and is quite exquisite.
But Sir Integra is...
It's been said, that General
Patton would stand alone,
braving the worst of blizzards
while watching his
soldiers on the march.
Patton's army was also reputed
to have nearly
unnatural stamina.
Do I make myself
clear, Miss Victoria?
A commander with
an indomitable spirit
can make a soldiers heart...
...burn like fire.
What is that?
Well, we seem to
have a guest. Excellent!
It's only proper for
you to have an escort
to take you to see your father.
What's that?
It moved!
Mr. Hellsing, what is that?
I don't know!
There is no record of this!
My brother never mentioned it!
A Vampire!
Is this how you protect me?
Shoot him! Kill him!
Send him back to hell!
My God!
Father, what were you
trying to accomplish?
You are the one who
has disturbed my rest.
Don't come any
closer to me! Monster!
Your sweet blood was the first
I've tasted in
over 20 silent years.
Those souls who suffer
their righteousness
will know their
eternal inheritance.
Vile demon!
I am the Lord and Master
of the Hellsing family!
Integral Wingates Hellsing!
I would die before allowing
a vampire to order me!
That gun is useless against me.
Give up little girl,
and listen...
Shut up! I'll never give up!
I'll die before giving up!
That is my duty and pride as the
leader of the
Hellsing organization!
Wonderful! Just wonderful!
You make my blood boil!
You are your father's daughter!
Forgive my
impertinence Sir Hellsing.
Your orders, my master?
Ridiculous!
The brat and the beast! Damn it!
I am the leader of
Hellsing! Hellsing is mine!
Your blood rots.
You are not the
master of this house.
But I...
What's your name?
Alucard.
That is the name
my last master used.
I was such a child back then.
You will always be
that same little girl to me.
Thank you.
Do you know who
I am, Sir Integra?
Doctor Trevelain...
You're going to be just fine.
Al...uca...rd!
Tada! Next, on a very
special episode of Hellsing...
I'll trade you tissue paper
for an episode preview.
What are you
talking about, Walter?
Here's your tissue.
That's not much tissue.
Not much of a preview.
Ugh...