I am so fucking hard right now!
We are smarter than you
bitches and you can't stop us!
We must defend the
third floor at all costs!
God, they're already this far.
You know, the security in
this place is so fuckin' weak!
What to do?
Old people's blood
taste like a shit.
But, it's no fucking fun
if I just shoot you...
Ferguson! Come in!
Ferguson!
Integra, what in hell
is going on out there?
We're under attack by
an unknown group.
Our field units
are pushing them back
at this very moment.
H...hello, is this thing on?
Alright, this is a shout
out to all our listeners
in the round table conference!
And a special hello
to that whoring little bitch
Ms. Hellsing, can you hear me?
We are the Valentine Brothers!
I'm Jann Valentine! And it's
real nice to finally meet you!
We appreciate you joining
us for this late lunch,
We are currently
enjoying the delicious taste
of the Hellsing membership.
They're eating... my people...
While you're waiting
for us to kill you,
we highly recommend
pissing yourself.
Followed by a course of
praying to your impotent God.
Then, cowering in the corner
and begging; always good!
But if you act now
there's still time
for an old fashioned suicide.
Good Lord.
Thank you London,
we love you, goodnight!
Well, looks like you
get to go first, old man!
What...the fuck...?!
Bloody pig!
Commander! You all right?
How's our unit?
I've been busy
helping the wounded
who won't turn into ghouls so...
I don't know.
I'm staying here.
What are you talking about?
I believed that men alone
could conquer all the
world's monsters.
I'll listen to your story later.
What the fuck?
I thought that Alucard
guy was the only one.
Now what?
Are we going to allow ourselves
to be slaughtered like this?
No, emergency escape
procedures are already in place.
Isn't that right, Sir Integra?
A helicopter is prepped
and standing by
at the top of the tower.
Then let's go!
We have no time to lose,
and we can't stay here!
We wait!
This room is protected
by 15 mm lead armor.
However, once
outside of this room,
there's no way
I can protect 11 people
from the Ghouls all by myself.
Then what do we suppose to do?
Mr. Ferguson has
probably already reported
the situation to the
proper authorities.
Once they discover that
they can't contact us,
they will mobilize.
W...what was that?
They've just destroyed
our helicopter.
Our enemies must have
really done their homework.
It's inappropriate to
be congratulating them.
Ghoul soldiers tenacity
makes them useful,
But, a special job
requires a special touch.
Jann, are you there?
Hey man! This is Jann,
captain and leader
of the Hellsing killer unit.
Oh, yeah!
Anything wrong?
No, nothing really.
But check this shit.
We gotta another undead sucker
to worry about
other than big red.
But she's like gone
underground though.
I understand.
I will take care of that.
Hey! I been working
my ass off bro.
First and second
floors are already clear.
Now all there's
left to take care of
is that stupid little bitch
and the old fucking geezer.
Oh, I guess there still
is one human left alive.
Master!
What are you doing here?
This is an emergency!
I'm waiting.
For the enemy?
They're all on the first floor!
My enemies are not the trash
that you've been
fighting, police girl.
Oh, is that right?
I'm surprised they managed
to get so many Ghouls inside.
The first floor is
completely overran and
now the second is almost lost...
And Sir Integra?
She's up stairs. Third floor.
We have to rescue her!
I was just heading up
there myself.
Would you care to accompany me?
The angel of death,
it's been too long.
The old dog and a new girl...
The two of us
make a perfect pair.
Angel of death?
Miss police girl, please bring
your nice new weapon with you.
Oh. Oh that...
Damn, that is so fucked up shit!
A country with
this much poverty,
and what does Miss bitch
spend her money on?
These fucking overpriced cigars.
Don't you boys think
that's pretty fucked up?
Of course you
thinks it's fucked up!
Death's too good for her!
I'm gonna fuck that bitch,
Shoot'er in'na head,
and then fuck her there!
They're getting
closer by the second!
So what do we do? Well? Anyone?
You've let them attack the nerve
center of this organization,
but now is not the
time to place blame.
We assume you have some
way to take care of this.
Of course, you do have
some kind of contingency plan?
Right?
Answer the man,
Integra Hellsing!
Relax gentlemen,
the real power of the
Hellsing organization
has yet to reveal itself.
Of course you're
speaking of the Vampires
whom you've trained
to kill their own kind?
Despite the fact that
you're true mission
is to kill them all.
This is no time
for you to be vague!
The ordeals of the first
masters of the Hellsing family
in the last century were
much harsher than this.
No matter how intelligent
or how strong they are,
they are still nothing
but vampire rubbish.
They will not destroy
the Hellsing family.
These monsters dare
to enter this house
built on blood and honor!
I will see all of them roasted
in the deepest pits of hell.
Damn! I don't believe I left
someone breathing on this floor!
Oh dear, I missed.
I suppose I'm not as
spry as I used to be.
Who the fuck are you old man?
Walter Dolnaise,
retainer of the Hellsing family.
And Hellsing organization
member, retired.
Shall we?
Boys, kill him!!
Too slow! You're far
too slow! Ghouls are fine,
but I have fought against
the true armies of the undead!
Don't push yourself,
Angel of Death.
It's about time!
Shit! Your fucked Gramps!
I most highly recommend
pissing yourself.
Followed by a course of
praying to your impotent God.
Oh yeah, yeah fuck yes!!
That's just what I want to hear!
I was getting so bored
of these easy kills, pops!
Ten hut!
Miss Victoria, please be a dear,
and lend some artillery back up.
Right!
For your next shot,
aim for the center
of the enemy battalion.
Use the incendiary shell
with VT bursting charge, 4 red.
Right!
There you are!
End of the line, Alfred!
Are you all right Walter?
Ouch! Ouch! That hurts!
A little out of practice,
but unscathed.
That was quite the
good tackle by the way.
Oh, well, I used
to be a cop you know.
You're not human neither.
God damn it!
Now, my boy, it's time
for some answers, all right?
Why did you try to
attack us so brazenly?
And who handed down the order?
You won't get shit from me, man!
You're late. I was
getting tired of waiting.
I do apologize.
I hope you find my company
was worth waiting for.
Because I've been waiting
for this for a long time.
My one on one with
the great Alucard!
It's time you found out,
just how good I am!
You're pretty fast!
Well of course I am!
I'm nothing like any
vampires you've fought before.
Because I am the vampire who's
going to put you in your grave.
Now why don't we
start on the other one?
May be...
Now you're going to tell
me who gave you your unlife
and who was responsible for the
freak chip implanted
inside your body?
Still think you can resist?
Your hapless little undead
army has been crushed.
You weren't trying to kill us,
instead you've turned all
of Hellsing into your Ghouls?
Great plan, no?
No...please, not again...
I don't want to
kill my own people...
Didn't I tell you?
I'm not like anything
you've met before!
I mean really.
What can you possibly do
against someone like me?
I have all of your
vampiric powers.
Actually I have far more
power then even that!
Why don't you fucking
eat this, bitch!?
Everybody...they've
all become Ghouls...
Miss Victoria!
N...no!
What fun! I haven't had
a fight like this in ages!
I truly applaud your
skill as a grade A vampire!
It can't be...I shot him
in the head...It's a trick.
I mean immortal maybe,
but nobody is that immortal.
Releasing control
art restriction to
level three, level two,
Situation A release level one!
The Cromwell approval
is now in effect.
Hold releasedd until
the target is silenced.
Now, I'll show you how
real vampires do battle!
Wait a minute...what
are you doing?
Where do you
think you're going?!
Did I say you could leave?!
Oh dear.
Let me go...
Miss Victoria?
Please make it stop!
What the hell are you!?
Stop whining! All I did was
to cut off your stupid legs...
Summon your servant demons!
Transform yourself!
Regenerate your
legs and stand up!
Pick up your gun and
attack on me! Do something!
The night is still so young, and
the real fun has yet to start!
Come on!
Come on! Come on! Come
on! Come on!....
M...monster! Oh, God!
You're a monster!
I see...you're...you're just
like the rest...
Time for you to die,
little Hellsing!
Miss Seras Victoria!
You're just like the rest.
Nothing but a disappointment...
You are nothing but dog food.
God damn bitch.
You gave me a hard time.
Stop laughing.
Fucking mercury
ignition bullets.
Give me the name of your master.
I won't allow you
to die until you do.
It's Janny...
...Luke...
...with the weather report.
Didn't we lose?
We sure did.
Hey bro, what's that weird
thing eating your head?
Ahhh...
And you're on fire.