I had a fabulous time tonight.
Seven and a half seconds
to set up the stock.
You're slow.
You won't be using that.
Why?
We both aware of what you are,
and won't you
be needing a scope.
Kim?
Christ, don't do that!
You alright?
There's something odd
about that woman over there.
Bit filthy, but not
hard on the eyes.
Wouldn't you say so, Kim luv?
I don't like the look of her.
Don't worry about it.
We're keeping Packstone
and the others waiting.
Please just humor me by trying
to have a good time tonight.
It's attacking civilians, sir.
In the name of god,
impure souls of the living dead
shall be banished into
eternal damnation. Amen.
Fire!
Gareth, Take the shot.
Mission completed.
Let's start cleaning
up the crime scene.
Roger.
I'm sorry sir.
Some say that failure
in your first battle
is a sign you'll live longer...
But I suppose you'll
live as long as you like,
or at least till your
sick of it anyway.
I suppose...
In the name of god,
impure souls of the living dead
shall be banished
into eternal damnation.
Amen.
Amen!
Victoria!
Yes sir?
I understand that when you were
an officer with Division 11,
they may have handled
you with kid gloves.
Well here the gloves come off.
I can't risk another
mission, therefore...
I don't need any
special treatment!
Mission or not!
I would like to
believe that, but...
Maybe you're too
highly strung for this.
Highly strung?
Ms. Victoria...
We will be taking care
of your day to day needs.
Huh? I... Well I...
This way please.
Excuse me...
We haven't been introduced,
my name is Walter.
I'm a retainer to
the Hellsing family.
Sir. Integra has asked
me to look after you.
Do I come off as
being highly strung?
Highly Strung? Well, that's
the least of your worries.
You've more to fear
from using a silver spoon.
Well, I've never used
real silverware before,
so I guess that
won't be a problem!
That didn't come out right...
I recommend that
you also refrain
from going out in daylight.
This is your room
for the daylight hours.
There's nothing quite
like a room with a view.
God, when I was a little girl,
I dreamed of having
a bed like this.
It's moving...excuse
me...what is this?
Oh, this is just a little
something to help you
sleep soundly during the long
daylight hours. Pleasant dreams.
A four poster coffin!
Bloody hell...
No more sleeping
at night I guess.
They work for me,
so don't feed off them.
I'm not like that!
I hope this doesn't
become a habit.
You and your little toy.
My toy? The police girl
made the choice on her own.
You just better
train her well, Alucard.
Here, take a look at this.
We've been tracking
some Hooligans
heading north
through Birmingham.
They've been murdering whole
families, drinking their blood,
and then using the
left over to scrawl
blasphemous
messages on the walls.
We're assuming there's
at least two of them.
They don't make vampires
like they used to.
I don't recall anyone
asking you for your opinion.
Well ... till tomorrow then.
This beats Ecstasy to
fuck-all, yeah Jessica?
Almost there baby...
Yeah.
Just nine more to go.
After we do nine
more of these cockers,
we're gonna be so much stronger.
And we can stay young forever!
Leif baby...
Yeah?
Want to?
The family's gonna
be ghoulies soon luv.
Who cares? Let'em watch.
Look at you, the bloods
got you fucked up!
Like your not?
Oh hell yeah...
This one just
might suit you better.
But, there's no way
I could even lift that thing!
Oh, I get it...
That's strange. What's
it made of? Is it plastic?
It weighs in 15 kilo's.
Plus a couple for ammo.
It's really that heavy?
The shot's no good.
That's fine for
dealing with humans
but for what we're
hunting, you aim for this...
...And nowhere else.
Capt. Gareth, prepare
your Unit for deployment!
Gareth's unit has set up a
blockade on the M6 motorway.
They should have our little
"Bonnie and Clyde" problem
dealt with inside of two hours.
Those two have no
idea what they've become.
Vampires, hardly
touched by the curse.
This is something the
world has never seen before.
Yes, I would have to agree.
Do you, wish you were out there?
I don't. I appreciate
the offer but
nothing satisfies me more
than serving you, Sir Integra.
Leif!
Whot?
You and me.
Together forever, right?
This is fuckin' super!
I never want this
feeling to stop! Ever!
We can love each other forever!
Whot?
Forever!
Target is confirmed.
Release the control
art restriction system
to level five.
We should be thankful for all
those stupid bloody meat-sacks,
They helped us get this bent up!
What?
What happened?
Leif baby, where are we?
Bloody Hell!
I don't know, all right?
I'm scared Lief!
Take me somewhere
else, right now!
Shut up! Just shut up!
Who the, hell?
Shit!
You're fuckin dead!
Children without faith.
If you had any control you
would travel as fog or as a bat.
Who the fuck, are you?
You've gone and
taken all those lives,
and not even because
you were thirsty.
Is it fun? Huh?
Is that what it takes for
filth like you to get off?
Cheap little two bit terrors.
What's it to you?
Eternity is wasted
on the likes of you.
Try as you might,
immortality slips away.
And you remain,
with only your shame.
Christ, Who is
this fuckin' cocker?
No! I don't like this!
That's enough for this shit!
Don't fail me this
time police girl.
Target B Acquired, and it's on
a clear path to your position.
500 meters and closing.
You should be able
to see her by now.
Sir... it's 500 meters...
My god...I can see her...
But she's... she's just a girl.
She can't be a vampire...
In the name of god,
impure souls of the living dead
shall be banished into
eternal damnation. Amen.
Shoot her Victoria.
It's time to prove
you're not just a monster.
Target acquired sir!
Now, Officer Seras!
Take the shot!
Target has been silenced.
Alucard shot and
silenced target A.
Senior officer
Seras Victoria, shot target B.
Roger, withdraw the unit.
Victoria!
Welcome to the
Hellsing organization.
Not bad, police girl.
I have a name.
It's Seras Victoria.
Not police girl.
You know that you
are now and forever
a child of the
darkness, police girl.
Drink the blood.
If you refuse to drink,
your body will become weak.
Do as I say.
Yes, Master.
Money falls...
...on the trees like leaves.
Hah!
So spend your money wisely.
Hey! Who the hell are you?