I'm sorry Mick. I know it hurts.
It threatens to
engulf me as well.
But from now on,
we can share it together.
Forever.
Oh my God...
Lord, Please give guidance
to this poor lost soul.
All I wanted, was for us
to always be together...
The Paris bound Euro-star train
will be leaving fifteen
minutes behind schedule.
Thank you for using Euro-star.
I'm sorry. Welcome
to London, Father.
Go with god my child.
Our subject is a
20 year old male.
Time of death is
approximately 72 hours ago.
However, the subject has been
mobile up until 12 hours ago.
I don't see any real
cell deterioration yet.
I'm making the first incision.
He was the son of
a noble Italian family
attending a local university.
We have to keep
this autopsy quiet.
You'd think his family would've
been instilled some discipline.
"Gentlemen don't drink
other people's blood.
Such behavior is
reserved for peasants."
Let's take a look shall we...
Right.
We've got one. The chip
is not functioning, though.
These chips are
becoming a problem.
Is it possible that this recent
increase in vampire activity
is part of some
larger unseen plan?
It still doesn't change the
Hellsing Organization's mission.
Search and destroy.
By the way lieutenant,
may I assume that you will look
into the boys known associates,
and his whereabouts
before the incident?
We've already begun
our investigation.
Right, stitch up the incisions.
Sir, isn't the protocol to
burn all our NHB remains.
This one doesn't belong to us.
He's a foreigner.
Someone from Rome will be
picking up his body later.
We pulled the bug.
He won't be a problem.
Yes sir.
God I'm tired. Dead, truly dead.
What do you think
you're doing police girl?
I'm sorry. But...
How many times
do I have to tell you?
If you don't drink,
you will become weak.
Your physical strength
should be far beyond
that of any normal
human being...
But just look at yourself.
I know that
I need it, it's just...
I hear your voice in
my head, it's not right.
I feel like I'm changing
into something so inhuman...
Master?
Hi!
God be with you child.
Humans creating vampires.
What do you think that says
about the world
we've created, Alucard?
I think it says that history is
full of man's cheap imitations.
Perhaps that's just your
true vampiric pride talking.
Tell me, what in essence
is the difference between
the true vampires we've
fought for centuries,
and these chipped
human creatures?
I know you're nothing
like those creatures.
It was uncalled for.
Then why did you
feel the need to say it?
You humans are incomprehensible.
You and the police girl.
Yes. I understand. Send them in.
Come in.
Mick. I just wanted
to be with you forever.
I know you understood,
Mick. Didn't you?
Answer me Mick. Please.
I can't see you. Where are you?
Mick, where did you go?
Stop!
Damn the Vatican and
their Section Thirteen bureau,
and damn the
Iscariot organization!
So far the London Police
have kept him in the basement.
But it's only a
matter of time before
the dead police become
ghouls and overpower them.
Even without the chip,
once they've been tainted
they will never human again.
I'm surrounded by idiots!
Hellsing Company A reporting.
We've prepped C-3 and are
now leaving for the crime scene.
May God and Her Majesty
be with you. Amen.
Amen.
GO! GO! GO!
Send over Alucard as well.
But this mission
hardly rates one vampire.
I will not repeat myself Walter!
Understood?
Yes.
This is a Protestant country.
I will not allow the
Vatican to run rampant.
Mick! Where are you?
Victoria.
Yes sir.
I want you to hold
your position here.
P7, going in!
I can do this...
What's going on? Norton!
My god...
Mick!
I hate that sound.
P7... they're all dead...
Captain Gareth.
What's it doing?
He's calling out
someone's name...
sounds like Mick...
Mick's body has
already been cremated.
When you fire,
make sure you only aim
for the heart or the head!
Master!
Those men inside that hospital
did not choose to become Ghouls.
And once they've been tainted,
There is no way for them
to ever be normal again.
The best that you have left
to offer them is a quick death.
Don't hesitate!
Yes sir, master.
Mick!
Your lover is not in
this world anymore.
It just... That didn't
happen...Captain Gareth!
Even with your
little humans friends,
you're still a
corrupted inhuman monster.
Poor Enrico Stivaletti's
soul is lost,
but his mortal remains
will at last find peace
at the hands of
this most sacred blade.
I shall now place
one more soul to rest.
Bastard...
I am the instrument of god.
Messenger of the divine
punishment of Heaven.
What?
You shouldn't have
come here, Catholic.
M-master...
Don't try to talk police girl.
Your body is weak.
Well now.
You must be the Hellsing
family's pet abomination.
You're from Iscariot. I see...
Iscariot was
ridding the world of
sacrilegious monsters
such as yourself
centuries before the
Hellsing family ever existed.
You defile this place.
I purify this house
so filthy creatures
can't use their
cheap black magic.
Our mission is to
punish any heretic
who would deny the word of God.
We will crush your unholy body,
and salt the earth
with your dust. Amen.
It's time somebody put
you in your place, human!
You've put a blessing on
that blade, haven't you.
This bullet was for a vampire,
But it'll do to send
you to hell father.
Master...
Weird little toy of
his actually hurt.
That sort of weapon can be
a real problem, even for us...
A Regenerator.
A human Regenerator...
I take an eye for an eye!
This Technology,
God's divine gift.
The lord gives us tools to
fight inhuman demons like you.
You're less than
inhuman, a pitiful defect,
a failed science project.
Sending you back to your
maker would be an act of mercy.
Your regeneration
power is very impressive,
But I bet if I put enough
bullets into your skull,
you'll stay down for good.
So let's cut to the chase.
Start begging.
Empty threats of
a coward vampire,
who hides behind
the weapons of man!
That's enough,
Paladin Alexander Anderson!
You don't have the
authority to command
one who's a true servant of God.
I said, "That's enough"!
Now Enrico Stivaletti
has been silenced.
Your mission in our
country has come to an end.
Your business
has been concluded.
Well, that's funny, I thought my
business was killing vampires.
You've already
exceeded your authority.
And you will suffer
the consequences
of your actions today.
New orders from the Archbishop.
The Archbishop has ordered you
to return to
Vatican immediately.
You will leave by the good
graces of Her Majesty.
I look forward to
the next time we meet,
Sir Integra Wingates Hellsing.
There's no room in the
Hellsing family for a vampire
that gets pummeled by
a Regenerator, Alucard.
Nor do we need a
half-starved vampire.
who can't protect
her own commander.
Understood?
I'm sorry sir.
Master...Alucard...
Police girl, you
must drink my blood.
Drink my blood,
Only then will you be free
of your servitude to me.
Once you are free, you will
be ready to become true family.
You won't,
be my master anymore...
No I won't. But you will
become a master of the undead.
You will drink blood and
walk the night by your own will.
Now drink my blood,
Seras Victoria.
So this is what you
choose police girl?
I don't know. I'm not ready.
Although, right now...I
know, I'm just...
There once was a
priest with a blade...
That's not a preview!
We just saw that guy!
He did weird things to
men and then stopped only
when in the parasite
palace he prayed.
Oooh! I like that place!
Really?