What do you want
on such a night?
Wha...what're you doing? Don't
come in without permission!
Bastard! What kind of
right do you people have
to enter somebody's
territory so rudely?
Who's the leader?
Give a proper greeting!
We secured the scene.
We're also holding evidence.
Stop! You can't touch it!
What is so illegal about it?
There are 74 candidates
up for membership.
Times being what they are,
we've extended offers
to foreign specialist
with good references as well
as the usual D11 and SAS crowd.
I trust you.
We found a report from
one of our embassy men.
They found a
factory in Hong Kong
that has been producing
quantities of the freak chip.
The Hong Kong Police
executed a compulsory
investigation into
the matter, but...
Everything was destroyed,
including any possible evidence.
Once again,
our hand is blocked...
Allowing heathens
and atheists membership
into our honorable organization.
Such a thing is without
precedent in the family,
but I do understand
we have no choice.
Even drawing from the SAS,
we won't acquire many skilled
soldiers worthy of our trust.
However, at the present
time, a show of force is
more important than trust.
Yes, Sir Integra.
I hope at the very least,
this group will be
strong enough to
avoid becoming ghouls.
I'll see to it personally.
Right, group seven.
Let's move on to you lot.
As you heard in the
briefing, when you encounter
threatening targets,
shoot only for the head.
Hits to other parts of
the target won't be counted.
If you shoot a
non threat target,
you will fail immediately,
and the test will end.
The arrows will help
guide you through the course.
Questions anyone?
Hey girl!
What is it then?
We heard some crap about there
being a real
vampire in this unit.
Have you?
Oh, it seems there's
something wrong with your MP5.
Uh...What do you mean?
Hullo, the barrel's bent.
You'd better go have
it replaced quickly,
or else you'll miss
your chance to test.
Chopper-1 to headquarters.
We found the suspect's vehicle.
It got rolled out in
the middle of the desert.
Our suspect looks
to be pretty dead
and still in the front seat.
"Artificial vampirisation
catalyst semiconductor.
The Freak Chip".
The semiconductor
hardware combined
with biotech theory and
what can only be described
as "A low amperage current
transmission device".
Thus far, the actual human to
vampire metamorphosis process
remains a total mystery.
So elusive is this process,
a hasty person would say it
borders on the supernatural.
Yes...well...
So potent is the elusive
"Freak effect" that one chip
is all that is necessary
to effect a single organism.
Our present leading theory
is that the chip somehow acts
upon information
latent in human DNA.
Er...Bear in mind,
however, this is all theory,
and not the only one
currently being considered.
Your findings are irrelevant!
Throughout history our
Hellsing organization
and Hellsing family,
have been detecting,
hunting and destroying those
creatures that have posed
a threat to Her Majesty,
the country and it's citizens.
And now, we face
these artificial freaks.
A freak is a freak whether they
were made artificially or not!
But consider this. The enemy
gave up their own factory.
The enemy sacrificed
the chip designer's life,
All because they feared that any
physical evidence would
eventually lead us to them.
Therefore...the enemy is human!
They're on the run now
that they sense a
predator at their heels.
We have only one
command and one mission!
To search and destroy!
Sorry daddy. I can't eat
these things anymore...
It's all wrong.
I finally became
a police officer...
And now...
God. Daddy?
Who's there?
I've come a long way to
see you, Seras Victoria.
Here.
Thanks.
I eh...missed tea
and supper today.
How did you know
to find me here?
Investigating things is
my job. As you well know.
Actually, I have know
idea who you are!
I apologize. My name's
Harry Anders. I'm with MI-5.
But why don't you
just call me Harry.
And what do you want with me?
Yeah, well before that...
would you mind if I had a
bite of that pie over there?
Go ahead.
Thanks, I love steak and kidney.
You understand this meeting
is not supposed to happen.
Despite the fact that
both of us is in or own way
are sworn to protect
Queen and country.
The differences are immense,
our agencies, our genders.
I'm human,
you're something else.
We're very different.
Exactly. This is delicious...
Cut to the chase.
What do you want with me?
You're observant.
A Copper thru and thru,
but then, so was your Dad.
How on Earth do
you know my father?!
Well... It was a long time ago.
I'll tell you about
it all some time.
But right now, there's a
place I need to take you.
No, no, you won't
be needing that.
I was just checking
mine because...
well being human
leaves me a bit vulnerable.
Who's there?
Helena, excuse me.
My name is Harry Anders,
and I work for MI-5.
May I come in? I just want to
ask you a few questions.
Just questions,
nothing more. I promise.
What are you doing?
Helena.
Good evening.
Good evening Helena.
Thank you for
making time to see me.
What?
Normally I do not entertain.
As I'm sure you know.
Your...one of us...
You've not been a
child of the darkness
for a particularly
long have you my dear?
You brought this
girl in the hopes that
she would shield you from me.
I must applaud you on
your cleverness, Mr. Anders.
Please forgive the ruse,
but I really wasn't
left with much choice.
Were you reborn
through carnal means,
or have you yet to
discover all the pleasures
of being a woman my dear?
Miss Helena,
you're...well...I mean...
when exactly did
you join the undead?
Far too long ago.
And you've always been
the way you are right now?
Yes, just as I am.
For forever, and forever.
Mr. Anders, I am a
very private individual.
And passive both by inclination
and ability, I am no threat.
As I'm sure your
investigations have shown.
So tell me why do you
insist on this harassment?
Yes, we're aware
that you're undead.
And while I wouldn't say
you're on the side
of the angels exactly,
you are a member of a
small Cabal of creatures
that don't threaten
the night world.
But, around 18 months ago,
a new breed of
night children appeared,
lacking the morals
and pride of your people.
They rampaged and
attacked my people,
turning many of
them into ghouls.
This girl,
Seras Victoria belongs
to the Hellsing organization.
No, but I only kill... I mean...
I...I've only disposed
of artificial freaks
like the ones Harry
was just mentioning.
Through all my long years...
Can you imagine how many friends
I've lost to your
Hellsing club's butchery?
I'm so sorry.
Unfortunately that apology
is not yours to give, child.
Now I understand...
the one who made you is
being kept by the
Hellsing Organization...
It's him...
Your speaking of my master?
You are much blessed,
Seras Victoria.
We've come to talk to you
of the dangers England faces.
Humans are using
machines to create
this new breed
of freak vampires.
They are not elegant
creatures such as yourself.
They are vapid greedy
things whose dark desires
are a twisted farce of humanity.
They are uncontrollably
violent and loud. Still...
Their power is not
even close to the
source of a true
vampire such as you.
This prattle wears
on my patience.
However, I will be willing
entertain your subject,
on the condition
that you will allow me
to return to my solitude.
Whenever you research
the chip design,
or discover a manufacturing
plant, it is destroyed.
As if someone is impeding
your investigation, correct?
Let's get to the point.
I may be with MI-5,
but I didn't come here on
any sort of official request,
and doubt they
would approve of it.
On the other hand, I believe
that God will forgive me
for noticing that our
interests run parallel,
and that maybe we
can help each other
work for the greater good.
Helena, I need
information you can provide
about you and your Cabal.
They may be
artificially created,
but they're still honest
to goodness vampires.
This investigation has been
leading me to the conclusion
that there might be
some sort of traitor,
amongst your compatriots.
Enough, Mr. Anders.
We have no such Cabal!
We are all individuals.
We are free from land,
country, religion.
All your petty forms
of human bondage.
Eternity is, however...a
very tiring existence.
I do not wish to leave
my home. As old as I may be,
I still have many books I am
looking forward to reading.
Anybody who disturbs this,
I do not count as a friend.
Humans forget the
nature of the world,
they treat it as property.
You must find
the Magna Mater...?
The first...um The Eve?
The primordial mitochondria?
Science was never
my strong-suit. I'm sorry.
My point is that man's
will alone is not enough.
Raw materials are
necessary for any creation.
To make a forgery, they must
have an original to forge.
An original vampire...
I've lived on this dark
Island for time out of mind.
It's my home.
No English Vampire is involved
in this madness,
of this I'm sure.
I understand...
Good evening, Ms.
Seras Victoria, Mr. Anders.
She seemed so
lonely didn't she...
Thanks a lot for coming with me.
I wish I could return the favor,
take you to dinner maybe...
Thanks for the thought.
So, I've heard you
don't drink fresh blood.
Just transfusion blood for me.
Christ if I was
twenty years younger...
Harry!
What?
Releasing control art
restriction system to level two!
Alucard!!!
Alucard...
Unlocking the power!
What the hell is going on?
Have you gone mad?
Haven't you ever
wondered Master...
how it feels to be hunted.
What's so damn funny?
Explain yourself!
What are you laughing about?
All the time I've
served you I have been
pitted against
pretenders and frauds.
But this time it's different.
A real enemy, a strong enemy
has finally come to
our tiny little island...
The true undead...
Perfect!
A battle unlike any other
before. Two genuine monsters!
Let him come!
All right, next
time on Hellsing is...
Meaty bullet battle!
Hallconnen and Jackall and
Walter goes shopping
for the first time.
Integra eats Fugu
sashimi and drinks 3 beers
I thought we talked
about your behavior?