(explosions booming)
(sirens blaring)
(slow dramatic music)
(upbeat music)
♪ Ah, ah, ah
♪ Did you lie
♪ On the stormy highway
♪ Did you dream
♪ Wheels spinning in the lonely night ♪
♪ Did you lie
♪ Millions of dreams, memories of yesterday ♪
♪ Little lies and illusions
♪ Did you dream
♪ Was my way of life
♪ Did you lie
♪ The howling wind strips them all away ♪
♪ Take, take, take my heart
♪ Big city standing here, we're heart to heart ♪
♪ Children lost seeking love and in the dark ♪
♪ Big city still surviving day by day ♪
♪ Will you ever ease the pain tears won't take away ♪
♪ Tears won't take away
♪ Tonight a hurricane
♪ Feel the hurricane
♪ Spending this lonely night loving you ♪
♪ Loving you
♪ Tonight a hurricane
♪ Touch me hurricane
♪ Show me your love with your touch ♪
♪ Burning touch
- [Dispatcher] Object heading west on 104th Street.
It's believed to be either an armored truck
or a light mobile armored combat machine.
All AD Police units in the vicinity respond immediately.
(sirens blaring)
♪ Did you lie
♪ I can never share the pain
♪ Did you dream
♪ Burning in your heart
♪ Did you lie
♪ If you keep saying everything is all right ♪
- [Woman] Massive explosion in District 14.
♪ No more streets in the pouring rain ♪
- [Woman] Police pursuit vehicles believed to be involved.
♪ Keeping us apart
♪ Did you lie
♪ Tell me how to help you through the night ♪
♪ Take, take, take my heart
♪ Big city standing here, we're heart to heart ♪
♪ Children lost seeking love and in the dark ♪
- Party time, babe.
♪ Big city still surviving day by day ♪
♪ Will you ever ease the pain tears won't take away ♪
♪ Tears won't take away
♪ Tonight a hurricane
♪ Feel the hurricane
♪ Spending this lonely night loving you ♪
♪ Loving you
♪ Tonight a hurricane
♪ Touch me hurricane
♪ Show me your love with your touch ♪
(gunshots banging)
♪ Burning touch
- [Officer] Target located, District 34.
- [Officer] 10-4, engage.
- Ready.
(gunshots banging)
♪ Big city standing here, we're heart to heart ♪
♪ Children lost seeking love and in the dark ♪
♪ Big city still surviving day by day ♪
♪ Will you ever ease the pain tears won't take away ♪
♪ Tears won't take away
♪ Tonight a hurricane
♪ Feel the hurricane
♪ Spending this lonely night loving you ♪
♪ Loving you
♪ Tonight a hurricane
♪ Touch me hurricane
♪ Show me your love with your touch ♪
(explosion booming)
♪ Tonight a hurricane
♪ Feel the hurricane
♪ Spending this lonely night loving you ♪
♪ Loving you
♪ Tonight a hurricane
♪ Touch me hurricane
♪ Show me your love with your touch ♪
♪ Burning touch
- You know, when Priss finds out this job is a freebie,
she'll be angry.
- This Boomer's acting in a most unusual manner.
- [Officer] Leon, he got past the District Nine gate.
Heading south on 42nd Street.
Choppers and drivers in pursuit.
- I got it.
- [Officer] Be careful.
There's something different about this one.
Maybe we should call in the army.
(tires squealing)
(sirens blaring)
- Some party.
Oh great.
(gunshot banging)
(dramatic music)
(gunshots rattling)
- [Officer] We've lost chopper two.
- Negative target contact.
(gunshots rattling)
(pilot screaming)
(explosion booming)
(gunshots banging)
- What a mess.
(interface beeping)
(gunshots banging)
(Boomer growling)
(upbeat music)
♪ Heartbeat of a cold, hard city ♪
♪ As the wind cries in mournful pity ♪
♪ Lonely, can you feel the fear in the night ♪
♪ Also seeking thought salvation ♪
♪ Voices screaming in desperation, help me ♪
♪ Help me find the way to the light ♪
♪ Once whispered cries echoed through the skies ♪
♪ A futile call
♪ Then who came through, it came from you ♪
♪ Save us all
♪ We want you, soldier girls (gunshots banging)
♪ Soldier girls
♪ Pierce the dark clouds above us ♪
♪ In the black night (gunshots banging)
♪ We want you soldier girls, soldier girls ♪
♪ Steel us within your armor
♪ Give us new sight
♪ We want you soldier girls, soldier girls ♪
♪ Courage drawn from the truth that's inside ♪
- - [Sylia] This is a totally new, highly advanced design.
♪ No turning back, no place to hide ♪
- What are they up to? ♪ May you ride
♪ We know you'll be on time
(explosion booming)
- [Sylia] It's a C-Class Boomer.
- A new type? - Looks that way.
Let's get out of here.
- Ah, so these are the infamous Knight Sabers.
Man, I am starved.
Guess the bad guys are just gonna have to wait.
Huh, is it Priss?
It is you, isn't it?
Fancy meeting you in a place like this.
I'm a big fan of yours, you know.
- Thanks.
- Hey, I caught your show this evening.
It was incredible.
Say, how about having a burger with me?
- I've already got one.
- Huh, oh, I see.
Well still, this is so cool.
I mean, me making friends with you.
Oh, I haven't introduced myself yet.
I'm Leon, I'm in the AD Police Boomer Crimes Division.
- I knew that from the badge on your chest.
You know, I hate the police, especially the AD Police.
- Hmm? (laughs)
Yeah, well there aren't many people
who say the really love the police.
- Well, people might like you better
if you actually helped them out once in a while.
Here, throw this away.
- [Leon] If I do, will you have dinner with me sometime?
- [Priss] Go cuddle with your Boomers, cop.
Who knows, maybe you'll get lucky.
- Hmm.
- Commander, these are the Knight Sabers.
- [Commander] So are they mercenaries?
- [Man] At least partially.
Their goals are unknown, but our intelligence suggests
they do accept commissions.
- [Commander] To think that such suits actually exist.
I would very much like to acquire them for analysis.
- You mean you want to hire them, sir?
- We can't let it become public knowledge
that this latest fiasco involves a USSD military secret.
Let's offer them a job.
- [Man] Yes, sir.
- Trade friction, you say?
The international communities want GENOM's products so much
they're fighting over them.
That's true.
GENOM accounts for 68% of the world's cars for example.
Relax, military combat Boomers,
they are not subject to discussion.
The balance of trade depends on Boomer sales
to countries involved in the pull of war, you know.
They're contributing to our country's continuing prosperity,
and we're proud of it.
Now can I count on your support in this matter?
If so, I'll guarantee the prime minister's position.
Yes, he'll be secure, count on it.
- Regarding the collection you desired, sir.
My men have just obtained it from USSD.
- With those items in hand, GENOM's future is assured.
I would appreciate a timely delivery.
I trust you understand me.
- I believe I can make it available to you
within 24 hours, sir.
- Mason, I'll leave this in your hands.
But don't forget that GENOM is a respectable company.
It would be unfortunate if our name
were to surface even slightly.
- Yes, sir, I'm aware of that, sir.
(water splashing)
(phone ringing)
- [Man] Hello, Uisu Laboratory
- Good evening. - Oh, good evening.
Chief, it's your daughter.
- Hello, is that you, Daddy?
- What's the matter, Sylia?
It's the middle of the night.
Why are you still up?
- It's been a whole week, Daddy.
When are you coming home?
I'm all right, but Mackie's feeling kind of lonely.
- [Katsuhito] I understand, Sylia.
You know I'm doing some very important research
right now, don't you?
- [Sylia] Yes.
- [Katsuhito] Be patient just a little longer.
- Secondary power source is online, sir.
- [Katsuhito] Set output logging to 10 hertz
and inject power.
This is only a simple prototype, but it's clear
that this technology will have endless applications.
(sirens blaring)
(explosions booming)
(Sylia gasps)
- Sis, this just came for you.
- Hmm, a data unit.
For me?
(Sylia gasps)
(bird chirping)
All right already.
(Sylia yawns)
(tranquil music)
- [Mackie] Sis, ready or not, here I come.
- Quiet, it's still early.
- Which paper are you reading?
Here, get a load of this.
- [Sylia] A job offer.
- [Mackie] You betcha.
- To the Knight Sabers, a consultation is requested.
(blow thudding) (Mackie groans)
- Oh (giggles).
Wow, look at this, isn't it radical?
- Save it for later, work comes first.
- Huh?
- Good afternoon, ladies, may I help you?
- [Linna] Do we have a job?
- [Sylia] How about something like this?
- [Nene] Oh, let's see.
- [Linna] Wow, 20 million up front.
(Nene gasps)
- Quiet.
- I mean, do these panties go for 20 million?
- Brilliant recovery.
- Have you finished investigating the client?
- [Sylia] It's USSD.
- USSD, the space defense force?
- This is a bunch of bullshit.
There has got to be a catch somewhere.
- You're right.
- [Linna] But I think that since we have an offer,
we should take it.
It's work after all.
- On the other hand, it just might be a trap.
- [Linna] That's true.
- What do we do, Sylia?
- I think there's merit in both your viewpoints.
We need to know the details of the job
and what they're really after.
Anyway, let's contact them right away.
Nene. - Hm?
- You're through with work for the day, aren't you?
Come with me.
- Okay.
- Hey, what's this? - What's going on?
- [Passenger] Watch your heavy metal.
- [Nene] Was getting on the bus dressed like this
really a good idea?
- [Sylia] You know what they say, dress for success.
(Nene groans)
Good afternoon.
- Huh, who are you?
- [Nene] Good afternoon.
- Combat suits, what do you want?
- [Sylia] We're the Knight Sabers.
We're here at the commander's invitation.
- What?
Hang on a second, I'm checking this out.
Hello, this is gate two.
I've got people claiming to be the Knight Sabers.
Yes, yes, that's right.
Huh?
Yes, sir.
My apologies.
The commander is waiting for you.
- See. - Yup.
- [Man] Sir, the Knight Sabers are here.
- [Commander] Ah, send them in.
- Huh?
Do you always dress like that?
- [Sylia] Of course, it's a dangerous world we live in.
- What, a woman?
- [Nene] Well, not even wearing armor can hide
these measurements, see what I mean?
- Ah, but they perform so wonderfully, don't they?
And they're so beautiful.
Ah, pardon me.
Since we are tentatively offering you a job,
we did a little research first.
To be frank, your suits are superior
to our own K-12 armored troopers.
They provide superb protection at a low mass penalty
and augment your agility.
Now what guarantee do we have that you'll keep the details
of this job confidential?
- [Sylia] Discretion is an essential part of our service.
If you don't trust us, don't hire us.
(Commander laughs)
- Quite right.
Let me explain.
FG Frederick, age 25, a computer technician with USSD.
Name Cynthia, age six.
I want you to find these two for me.
- [Nene] Tracking down missing persons?
What's so special about this girl?
- Well, you see--
- [Sylia] Okay, fine.
But I can't believe this is a mere missing persons search.
- The girl was abducted yesterday,
and our investigation indicates that the abduction
was performed by a group of Boomers.
And Boomers are your specialty.
- [Sylia] What else do you know?
- [Man] Well, we think Frederick infiltrated us on some
unknown person's orders and, as a member of our staff,
was able to mastermind the operation.
- [Sylia] Then this Frederick is a Boomer too?
- [Man] That's something we can't confirm now.
- [Man] Bring up the temperature display.
- [Sylia] So what are they after?
- Well, they demand to know the secrets of an exotic weapon
which holds the key to our nation's defense.
- [Sylia] The ion particle beam platforms?
- You know of them?
- [Sylia] Range versus target alignment error
10 to the negative 10th.
Capable of destroying an area up to 1,000-kilometer radius.
- [Commander] You are good.
- [Sylia] It disgusts me to think that there are over 200
of those things floating over my head.
- Yes, but you certainly understand that they are necessary
for national security.
As you know, even third world countries
possess satellite weapons, so the IPBPs--
are a regrettable-- - Sylia, that's no ordinary
camera pointing at us, look. - But necessary evil.
Without them it'd be impossible to maintain
the balance of power. (gun zapping)
(static buzzing)
- Whoa, please, please, wait.
We apologize, honestly, you must forgive us.
We really do want to hire you for this.
- Yes, in fact if you can discover who is behind
the abduction, we'll pay you an additional 20 million.
- [Sylia] We're not being tailed, are we?
- [Nene] Looks safe, but heaven knows.
(ominous music)
- [Sylia] It's getting so you so can't
trust anybody these days.
(laser buzzing)
What are you doing?
- [Nene] Letting them know what I think.
(computer beeping)
- [Sylia] We add together last night's Boomer rampage
down 42nd Street and this new job, what do we get, Nene?
- [Nene] I wonder if that Boomer wasn't a decoy
meant to confuse the AD Police.
- [Sylia] Based on our analysis of the AD Police data
Nene's gathered and our quarry's movements last night,
for the time being we'll concentrate
on Districts 10, 11, and 12.
Okay, let's get started.
Remember to check in frequently,
and don't attempt any rescue alone.
- [Priss] All right, already.
(upbeat music)
- [Man] Never seen 'em before.
Did the old man and the brat run out on you? (laughs)
- It's not like that at all.
(dramatic music)
- Someone's looking for you and Cynthia.
- Thanks for the information.
- It was a woman, not a bad-looking woman either.
What, out of brew?
Who do you think she is, Bogey?
- [Bogey] I don't know.
How about we take her for a ride and let her tell us?
(door creaks) (Priss gasps)
- Just who the hell are you?
(Bogey laughs) Boomers.
(blow thuds) (Priss groans)
- Who the hell is she, AD Police?
- No, Bogey, I don't think that she's the police.
- [Bogey] Fine with me.
We'll get it out of her in due time
when we get to Aqua City.
- Aqua City.
- [Bogey] The others are probably there already.
- Yeah. (dramatic music)
(metal crunching)
(glass shattering)
(Priss groaning)
- Ow, shit.
Don't you assholes even know how to have an accident?
(explosions booming)
Thanks for the directions.
(Priss gasps)
I'll bring it back.
(jets humming)
(tires squealing) - Boomer.
(sirens blaring)
(engine revving)
- [Sylia] Here you go.
- Oh no, no more for me.
My stomach's gurgling.
- Do you think something's happened to Priss?
- [Sylia] She is a little late, isn't she?
- [Nene] That's typical.
- How many times have I told her to call in regularly?
She just doesn't listen.
(static buzzing)
- Nothing, just patrol messages.
Looks like the Boomers have the night off.
Hold on. (static buzzing)
- [Officer] Calling station one.
This is ADP 102 calling station one.
I'm in pursuit of a Boomer on route K-5 heading for R-51.
Subjects are a C-Class Boomer and a racing bike.
- A racing bike?
That must be Priss.
R-51, that's Aqua City.
Let's check it out.
- [Sylia] No, it could be anyone, not just Priss.
- That's true.
All we can is wait for her to contact us.
- [Nene] But if it is Priss, she won't have her suit.
- She could be in trouble.
Damn, this worries me. - Mhm.
- If only she'd hurry up and give us a call.
- Mhm.
- Sis?
Yeah. (girls laugh)
(tires squealing) (sirens blaring)
(ominous music)
(gun clicking)
(footsteps pattering)
- Hmm, a map of Tokyo.
Cynthia, don't be frightened.
Are you Cynthia?
- Mhm, who are you, lady?
- I'm Priss, I've come to rescue you.
Oh look, you've gotten your clothes all dirty.
Are you alone? - Uh huh.
- [Priss] Well, is anyone else here?
- Uh, I don't know.
Look at this, lady.
- [Priss] Huh, what the?
I've seen that drawing somewhere before.
- I did that.
- Oh, I see.
Well, you're very talented.
Come on, let's go home.
I'm sure your mom and papa must be worried about you.
- I have no such people.
- What the, huh?
What the hell's going on here?
(footstep echoing)
(Priss gasps) (dramatic music)
(engines revving)
(blow thudding) (Priss groans)
(Priss shouts)
(Priss groaning)
- (laughs) My, my you actually managed to scratch him.
We ought to make you pay for the repairs.
- How about I roast her?
- [Woman] Hold it, after she's told us who she works for.
- Why bother?
Let's just kill her now.
(gun clicking)
(gunshots banging)
(woman shouting)
(gunshots banging) (woman groaning)
(Priss gasps)
(woman retches)
- You've got one round left.
You gonna use it?
Looks like you're gonna have to foot the bill
for fixing me too. (laughs)
(Priss breathes heavily)
So you still don't wanna talk, eh?
Soon you won't be able to, even if you wanted to.
- We've shown you nothing but kindness,
but you still won't chat, eh?
- Oh, it's you.
- That's right, the man you've been looking for.
Seems they told you I was a computer technician, but--
- You're a Boomer too.
Why'd you choose that girl for this project?
- [Frederick] Apparently you know
nothing at all about Cynthia.
- What?
- [Frederick] I don't know which
intelligence agency sent you.
But if you don't intend to talk,
your usefulness is at an end.
(Priss groaning)
- Lady?
(woman laughs)
(gunshot booming)
(upbeat music)
- Who the hell are you?
- [Sylia] The Knight Sabers.
- So what, are we supposed to be impressed by that?
(explosion booming)
(metal clanging)
(Boomers thudding)
- Oh, not bad
I'd say you're superior
to the military's K-12 armored troopers.
You really did a number on my friends.
What do you hope to accomplish?
- [Sylia] To defend peace and justice
and rid the world of evil.
- A worthy objective,
but to achieve it you must first defeat me.
(dramatic music)
- [Sylia] Get the girl out of here, hurry.
- After them, don't let them get away.
(gunshots booming)
(Frederick laughs)
(gunshot banging) (Frederick shouts)
(gunshot banging)
- Well, Priss, I guess this means our date is on.
- Cut the crap, I just want to get the hell out of here.
Which way?
- Uh oh, go that way.
- Thanks. - Yeah.
(Boomer roaring)
(gunshots banging)
(ground rumbling)
- Oh, damn.
- Lady, oh, help!
- Cynthia!
Damn it!
(explosion booming)
- What the?
- [Sylia] This is a Boomer?
- [Nene] That's impossible!
- Priss, what happened?
Get in, I've got a med kit in front.
Priss, what are you...
Hey.
(Sylia groaning)
You won't stand a chance in your condition.
(dramatic music)
(explosion booming)
- I went to a lot of trouble to find her.
I will bring her back.
(ground rumbling)
- [Sylia] All of Aqua City is becoming part of his matrix.
It's hopeless.
(Boomer roaring)
- Looks like the Knight Sabers have bitten off
more than they can chew.
- [Priss] Sylia, did you miss me?
- [Sylia] Priss.
- [Priss] Here I go.
- [Sylia] Go for it.
(explosion booming)
(metal crunching)
(gunshot banging)
(gunshots banging)
(explosion booming)
(Boomer groaning)
- [Nene] We did it.
- [Sylia] You okay?
(Cynthia screams)
(computer beeping)
- [Linna] What's with that chopper?
- GENOM. - GENOM, hm?
- [Linna] It's Cynthia, she's a Boomer.
(dramatic music)
(laser zapping)
(explosion booming)
- [Sylia] The satellite weapons.
- Help me!
(explosions booming)
(water rushing)
- Hey hey, do you suppose we can collect the balance
under the circumstances?
- That's right.
- Don't you realize how serious this is?
- Oh, I realize.
20 million, 20.
- [Priss] That's not what I mean.
- [Linna] What do you mean then?
We're talking 20 million here.
- [Nene] I'm exhausted.
- Okay, let's get out of here.
(Leon breathing heavily)
- Priss!
Sorry to keep you waiting so long.
I mean for our first date.
- I wasn't waiting for you.
- Say no more.
Let's go out to dinner.
How about it?
- You actually did something
that helped people for a change.
Thanks.
- Hey, where you going?
I wonder if she's a...
Oh well.
(sirens blaring)
(upbeat music)
♪ Hustle and the bustle
♪ Working in the city
♪ Daylight keeps our fears at bay ♪
♪ Sunshine breaks the gloom, heartbeats dodging doom ♪
♪ Hoping for another day
♪ If we're bound by invisible schemes ♪
♪ Then all our dreams are our only impression ♪
♪ Hey Mr. Dandy, hey Mr. Joy
♪ Can't find love's key
♪ Lights fading, I cannot see
♪ Hey Mr. Dandy, hey Mr. Joy
♪ Feels like lost love's
♪ Gripping your heart so tightly ♪
♪ Cool enchanted ocean calming the commotion ♪
♪ On an endless summer day
♪ Colors in the city, nighttime has no pity ♪
♪ Wish the light would always stay ♪
♪ But the dark shadows will fall ♪
♪ Drowning us all in a sea of depression ♪
♪ Hey Mr. Dandy, hey Mr. Joy
♪ Can't find love's key
♪ Lights fading, I cannot see
♪ Hey Mr. Dandy, hey Mr. Joy
♪ Feels like lost love's
♪ Gripping your heart so tightly, yeah ♪
♪ Hey Mr. Dandy, hey Mr. Joy
♪ Can't find love's key
♪ Lights fading, I cannot see
♪ Hey Mr. Dandy, hey Mr. Joy
♪ Feels like lost love's
♪ Gripping your heart so tightly ♪