(\"Mad Machine\")
(upbeat rock music)
♪ Mad machine
♪ How, when we cross the plains ♪
♪ Low raging sandstorms deliver me ♪
♪ Hey, hey
♪ Mad machine
♪ I always catch my prey
♪ Two screaming wheels are my destiny ♪
♪ Hey, hey
♪ Mad machine
♪ There's just no logic to
♪ This fire that burns in my heart for you ♪
♪ Hey, hey
♪ Mad machine
♪ Whenever I'm with you (machine beeping)
♪ Sharing the same dream, connect the two ♪
♪ Hey, hey
♪ I know what I want, what I really need ♪
♪ I don't wanna cool down your fire ♪
♪ Until all my sadness is torn all to shreds ♪
♪ You're all that I'm dreaming of ♪
♪ Don't stop your love
♪ Your love
♪ Tell me, what do you want
♪ Tell me, how do you feel
♪ Cold, angry child, wounded and wild ♪
♪ Seeking the blood of our rival ♪
♪ You and I ride, raging inside ♪
♪ Challenging them for survival ♪
- [Reporter] An accident occurred
at about four o'clock this morning.
A USSD orbital particle beam satellite
discharged by mistake,
striking the Tokyo Bay Aqua City
and sending it up in flames.
In addition, according to a police statement.
♪ Heart stops in fear
♪ Nothing is clear
♪ Each time, my head is turning ♪
♪ Tell me, what do you want
♪ Tell me, how do you feel
♪ Mad machine
♪ What will tomorrow bring
♪ We can't be sure about anything ♪
♪ Hey, hey
♪ Mad machine
♪ You give me what I need
♪ Someone to run with who'll let me be ♪
♪ Hey, hey
♪ Everything was real
♪ Now it melts away
♪ Plain such sad truth can be
- With regard to the Aqua City incident yesterday,
the accidental particle beam satellite discharge
was most regrettable.
USSD will therefore place
its full resources into an inquiry.
We strive to prevent such an accident from occurring again.
♪ Tell me, what do you want
♪ Tell me, what do you need
♪ Time's not a friend
♪ Nearing the end
♪ Can we defend our freedom (sirens blaring)
♪ Wounded beasts screams
♪ Shattering dreams
♪ Charging in blind confusion
♪ Wild, angry cries
♪ Open my eyes
- [Man] No, you're wrong.
We're with the appliances department.
And besides, a patrol section showed up right away
and kept us from entering.
- [Daley] If you're covering something up
it won't do any good.
- But it's under the jurisdiction of the research
and development department.
It's got nothing to do with us.
- Really?
A bunch of useless, blind witnesses.
Now, get the hell outta here!
Hey, someone get the guys from the patrol section
and the research department down here.
And get everything in this room tagged.
(sirens wailing)
- [Linna] Hey, that girl.
- [Priss] You know her, Linna?
- [Linna] Yeah, from the aerobics club.
- You can't fool me!
You murdered him, I know you did!
(hand thwacks) (Irene screams)
- You sorry bitch.
Move it.
- Where do you think you're going, babe?
(knee thuds) (man groans)
- Hey, Carl, I bet that hurts.
- Damn you! (hand whacks)
Ow, shit.
(Priss groans)
You're a Boomer?
(Priss yells)
- Hold it right there, I'm Leon, AD Police.
Now, cut the crap or I'm taking all of you in.
- That's enough, let her go.
We don't welcome false accusations.
We consider our corporate image very important.
Now if you don't mind.
- Who was that?
- Brian Jane Mason.
He's the personal assistant to the chairman
of the Genom corporation.
A real snake.
- Hmm.
- [Man] Cynthia was a weapon we developed to synchronize
with the orbital satellites.
- [Sylia] She may have been just a weapon to you, but to us,
she was a little girl that needed to be rescued.
- [Man] During the design phase
we considered many possible shapes but--
- Do us all a favor and make the next one look like a dog
or a cat.
But we'll take the job, loose ends and all.
- [Man] We deeply appreciate it.
Here are the details of the assignment,
as well as data about Black Box,
the orbital satellite synchronization system.
- We will expect our 20 million fee upon completion.
So heartless.
(horns honking)
- Case closed?
(scoffs) It's more pressure from Genom, isn't it?
- Not at all.
Upstairs has already decided
that this was merely an accident.
There's absolutely no evidence of Boomer involvement.
- They haven't even been to the scene.
What the hell do they know?
- They know that your job is dealing with real Boomer crimes
so lay off this one!
- Come on, are you blind?
Genom is developing a monster Boomer.
- Bullshit!
That's just a hunch.
Anyway, nothing's really happened yet.
- What are you gonna do, just sit and wait for it?
- Get outta my face!
It's about time somebody starting reining you in!
- Listen, lard ass, any time you wanna consider disability,
just let me know.
- [Captain] Why you arrogant punk!
I'm gonna make you eat those words.
- (laughs) Are they at it again?
- [Cop] Yup.
- I swear it's all this political bullshit
that keeps us from doing our job.
- Oh, Leon, I can help you with that job,
but you're so tense.
I know just the thing,
there's this quiet little motel.
- Oh, yeah, Daley, someplace where we can be alone.
- [Daley] How 'bout your car?
- [Leon] Nah, an APC, it's roomier.
(officers laughing)
- [Sylia] Someone beat USSD to the Black Box
and recovered it from the wreckage of Aqua City.
I've got a hunch Genom's involved,
and that today's explosion is somehow related to it.
- (groans) Genom huh?
So we get another crack at 'em.
(grunts)
- But aren't they too big for us?
Besides, I'm not too keen on this payment on delivery stuff.
- I'm so sick of watching the AD Police screw up.
This is driving me totally insane.
- Well then the three of you should get started immediately.
Priss, you check out activities connected with Genom.
Nene, crack into the AD Police databases.
Mackie can help you with the passwords.
- [Priss and Nene] Okay.
- [Cop] Good morning, AD Police Investigation section.
Who?
Yeah, hang on a sec.
Hey, Leon, line two, pick it up.
- If it's a guy, tell him I'm not here.
- [Cop] It's a babe, name's Priss.
- Huh?
Hey, Priss, I can't believe it.
I feel so honored to get a phone call from ya.
- I'll go out with you.
- Huh, really?
When?
- [Priss] Today, at 11.
- If you wanna meet that late then let's meet a hotel,
and I know just the place.
- 11 in the morning, you jerk.
- [Leon] In the middle of the day?
I'm still on duty then.
- Make up something then sneak out.
Meet me at the Ragu Steakhouse on 26th.
Later.
- Huh?
Yesterday I'm scum,
today she can't wait to see me.
I must be cooler than I thought.
Boy, you can really put it away.
- [Priss] This is both breakfast and lunch for me.
Sure you won't have anything?
- [Leon] No, just being here with you is enough.
- Oh, come on, don't deprive yourself.
You're paying after all.
Delicious.
I saw on the morning news that you're investigating
last night's explosion.
- So did I look good or what?
- Not bad.
But what did they mean by case closed?
- Oh, that the brass have made up their minds.
But I disagree.
- Oh, you do?
- The way I see it there's something fishy going on
inside the Genom building.
Like the development of an advance Boomer, for example.
- An advanced Boomer?
- [Leon] Right.
- And that means.
- So, why are you so interested in all this anyway?
- Oh, I just kinda like this kind of stuff.
You know, it's like watching a science fiction movie.
So, the explosion was a project related accident?
- Uh-huh, some sort of screw up.
- Now that must mean that the development project
is still underway in the Genom building.
- When I was at the scene of the accident
one of their patrol guys told me
that a delivery truck left at the same time
as the explosion through a normally unused gate.
- You mean they moved to another location?
- Right.
- Would you look at the time?
This has been very interesting,
but I've got a show to do now.
- Hmm?
You can't do that.
So far all we've done is eat.
- Good luck hunting Boomers.
- Hey, hold on a second.
(register beeps)
Huh?
(groans)
(dramatic music)
(machine buzzing)
(monitor beeping)
(Sylia laughs)
(upbeat music)
- My boyfriend was an engineer
doing R and D on Boomers for use in space.
- It sounds like he must've been a really special guy.
- He always seemed happy
when he talked about his research projects,
but after he got involved with this project
he got very nervous about something.
- What was the project?
- He said it was some sort of a linkage system.
But he was scared.
Scared that if he said anymore he might be silenced.
- Oh no!
What about the police?
- We told them, but they wouldn't pay any attention.
If only I knew what really happened to him.
- [Linna] So that was why you did what you did?
- Yes.
It's just that as soon as this project was finished
we were going to be married.
Now this ring is all that I have left.
(light electronic music)
(tires screech)
I am feeling a little bit better.
- I'm glad.
You look better.
- Well, thanks.
But I'm still going to try to find out
what really happened to him.
- Find out?
(scanner beeping)
- What I discovered is that
because of the recent Boomer crimes
Genom will be a media target
since they produce the Boomers.
I'll try to expose what really happened.
- But, Irene, if you go to far it'll put you in danger too.
- Maybe so,
but I just wanna make some sense out of this.
Now if something does happen to me,
see that those vigilantes avenge me.
You will promise me that, won't you, Linna?
- Huh?
- [Irene] I'm only kidding. (laughs)
- That's not funny.
(Irene giggles)
I tell ya, that waitress really had an attitude problem.
What the?
My car!
- I'll walk home.
Besides, it's not that far.
And I'm kinda in the mood for it anyway.
- [Linna] Okay, be careful.
- Linna, I'm glad you're so concerned about me.
Thanks so much.
- See you tomorrow.
Oh, great, how do I get home?
(tires crunching)
(dramatic music) (engine revs)
(tires screech)
(car thuds)
Irene!
- Got it.
Mackie, contact Priss immediately.
We've got a problem.
- Okay, I've got it.
(communicator beeps)
(dramatic music)
- [Mackie] Priss, head for the Third Street corner
of Yokohama, Chinatown.
(dramatic music) (car rumbles)
(Irene yelps)
(tires screech)
(dramatic music)
(Irene pants)
(Irene sobs)
- Irene!
(Irene sobbing)
(dramatic music)
(Irene whimpers)
(Irene yelps)
Irene!
(dramatic music)
(Irene groans)
Priss, over here!
(tires screech)
(Linna gasps)
Irene.
- [Priss] Bitch!
- Priss, wait a minute.
Where do you think you're going?
I'll do this, this is my fight!
(dramatic music)
Irene, I'm sorry.
(elevator dings)
(intense electronic music)
- Mackie! (grunts)
♪ There is a place I know
♪ Where all my tears are wiped away ♪
♪ Frozen in the scarlet haze
♪ Far from the danger zone
(truck rumbles)
♪ Times of trouble fade
♪ My worries have no meaning
♪ Soon it takes away the fear
- [Mackie] There are four Genom laboratories
in the Kawasaki factory zone.
But two of them have been closed down.
Activity has resumed at one of them since the explosion
and according to AD Police data,
the truck that left by gate R headed straight from that gate
for Kawasaki.
- The closed laboratory seems suspicious.
It was a terrible place
with a history of research accidents.
It was finally shut down after 12 people died.
That was six years ago.
- [Sylia] Boomers I'll bet.
- [Mackie] They were allegedly developing power sources
for a new resin based, biomechanical fusion system,
but it must've been a cover up for Boomer related work.
(alarm blaring)
- Welcome Knight Sabers.
Join me as we toast the birth of a super Boomer.
(truck thuds)
(mechanical arm whirs)
- [Sylia] Knight Sabers, it's showtime!
(engine revs)
(dramatic electronic music)
- [Priss] Damn, a Boomer!
(Priss thuds)
(engine rumbles)
(Linna whooshes)
- [Nene] They're somewhere between
the third and fifth floors but I can't figure out where.
- [Linna] I don't expect them to stay in just one place.
- [Nene] Ah-ha, now I see.
- [Priss] Nene!
(Nene screaming) (lasers blasting)
(Nene grunts)
(Boomer thuds)
- [Linna] Nene!
- [Nene] I'm okay.
Owie, owie, owie!
(fists thudding)
(monitor beeps)
(upbeat music)
(gun blasting)
(Boomer whooshes)
(lasers blasting)
(metal clangs)
(upbeat music)
(fire whooshes)
(metal clangs)
(pipe whooshes)
(gun bangs)
(Boomer thuds)
(metal rattles) (suspenseful music)
Something's coming!
(Boomer growls)
(metal clangs)
(dramatic music)
- [Mackie] I'm picking up transmissions
on the same frequency that Cynthia used.
It's syncing to the particle beam satellites.
If I can't remove the satellite from the transmission
frequency I don't know--
- [Sylia] Mackie, calm down and see what you can do!
(dramatic music)
- [Priss] You bastard!
Go for its head.
(dramatic music)
(explosion booms)
(laser blasts)
(dramatic music)
- [Mackie] The particle beam satellites,
they lost target lock but they're still operational.
- [Priss] I don't believe it.
- [Mackie] Well you better believe it.
- [Priss] No choice, the knuckle bomb.
- [Mackie] The satellites, they're locking on target.
- [Priss] Linna, outta my way!
(dramatic music)
(explosion booming)
- [Mackie] The particle beam satellites
seem to be standing down.
- [Nene] The Black Box has gone up in smoke.
- [Linna] It's best this way.
- [Nene] Huh?
What about our 20 million, Linna?
(fire roars)
- [Reporter] Commander Schwartz of the scandal plagued USSD
announced his resignation a short time ago.
His successor.
(\"Kizudarake no Wild\")
(upbeat music)
♪ Shattered dreams
♪ Broken hearts
♪ That were once my crystal castles in the sky ♪
♪ Washed away
♪ By the tears, so bitterly I've cried ♪
♪ I'm not the only one
♪ In this sea of light
♪ Having pain in my heart
♪ Midnight dreaming
♪ There is no peace out in the angry city streets ♪
♪ I hear them stirring in my memory ♪
♪ They keep on calling
♪ I won't give in
♪ This race with time will never end ♪
♪ Those demons from the past tormenting me ♪
♪ Teardrops
♪ No longer hide the courage deep inside ♪
♪ I'm running free, I was born to be ♪
♪ Wild at heart
(upbeat music)
♪ We just seek love out in these angry city streets ♪
♪ Though unseen walls may try and block the way ♪
♪ They keep on falling
♪ I won't give in
♪ Because I know that in the end ♪
♪ Tenderness is the gift pain gives to me ♪
♪ Nevermind
♪ I've learned to fly with wings though weak and scarred ♪
♪ I'm running free, I was born to be wild at heart ♪