(electronic beeping)
(typing)
- The Type BU-12B Cyberdroid,
equipped with bazooka and 46 millimeter machine gun
is, according to internal sensor signals,
now crossing the Ring Line at Point M,
heading north toward District Three of Tinsel City.
It has arrived at Point K, Route 246,
where it is engaging the Sixth AD Police Mobile Force.
(intense music)
(exploding)
(fire crackling)
(whirring)
(gun banging)
(laser blasting)
- [Policeman] A Combat Boomer's appeared at Point K,
Route 246, District Three.
The Sixth AD Police Mobile Force is currently engaging it.
(police sirens wailing)
(exploding)
(gun banging)
- [Pilot] HQ, this thing's kickin' all kinds of ass.
I'm engagin' the K-11s.
- [Dispatcher] 10-4.
(rock music)
- [Man] How many times do I have to put up
with your standing me up?
You're due on stage any minute, Priss.
- [Priss] I told you, this can't wait!
- [Linna] Hurry up, Priss.
- [Priss] All right, all right.
- [Man] All right then, you'll never work here again.
You got that?
- [Priss] Terrific, now ask me if I give a damn.
- [Linna] I'm really sorry, sir,
but this is really an emergency!
- [Man] Shut the bloody door!
- Yes, sir.
- [Priss] Man, that Boomer's got a lot of nerve,
stomping around near Sylia's place.
- Apparently, it's a combat model.
The AD Police seem to be having a tough time of it.
- A combat type?
All right, I'll meet you there.
(bike revving)
- [Linna] Come on.
Oh, start!
(air whooshing)
(screaming)
(guns banging)
(laser blasting)
(cars honking)
- Wouldn't ya know it?
Just my luck to be on the early shift today.
(car honking)
Hey, you in that car!
Pipe it down, or else!
Ooh, they're about to drive me crazy.
- [Priss] Hey, officer, let me through!
- What is it?
Oh, Priss.
(bike revving)
- [Priss] Thanks, officer.
- [Motorcycle Cop] You idiot, why'd you let her through?
She's speeding.
- I'm sorry.
Oh, today just isn't my day.
(intense techno music)
(gun banging)
(glass shattering)
(bike revving)
(guns banging)
(thudding)
(glass shattering)
(guns banging)
(bike revving)
(gun banging) (gasping)
- Son of a bitch!
(tires screeching)
(gun banging)
(laser blasting)
(exploding)
(police sirens wailing)
(electronic beeping)
(engine revving)
(tires screeching)
(guns banging)
(thudding)
(tires screeching)
- [Motorcycle cop] You were 50K over the limit!
- Leon.
- Hey, babe, the law's the law.
- Big help you are.
(scoffing)
Man, this boomer's made a real mess.
Thanks to him, my license is being suspended.
- [Nene] Well thanks to you,
I'm in hot water with the traffic cops.
I'm really having bad luck.
- [Linna] I'm the one who's having bad luck.
My car died, and I had to take a cab.
- We can't let this slide.
It's that bastard Mason who's behind all this,
I'm sure of it.
Let's get off our asses and nail him.
- No, it's best if we leave this to the AD Police.
Just forget about it Priss, and give us a hand.
- Linna, you know, I'm not into that kinda stuff.
- [Linna] Oh, give me a break.
- That's not fair.
(laughing)
- Hey Priss, come outside for a sec.
Gotta surprise.
(bike revving)
- Man, this is sweet.
Is it ready to ride?
- [Leon] It should be okay.
(bike revving)
(tires screeching)
- Sho.
- Oh, Priss.
- Your mom's not back from work yet?
- Uh-uh.
- Oh, you must be hungry.
Here, why don't you have some of this?
- Oh boy, thanks, Priss!
(footsteps)
- Sho?
- Hi, mom!
- Let's go have dinner.
- Okay, what are we having tonight?
- Hamburgers.
- Mom, Priss already gave me a burger.
Let's have pizza instead.
- [Sho's Mom] All right.
Now, let's go home.
(door opening)
(footsteps)
(door closing)
(light clicking on)
(suspenseful music)
- More over,
the Boomer which terrorized the city was a combat model.
This type of manufacturing is illegal in Japan.
Citizens' groups are demanding
stricter enforcement of the law.
In other news around the globe,
the widely expected merger of Uldo Enterprises.
- [Priss] Hey, Linna.
Why the hell won't Sylia take a shot at him?
- Huh?
At who?
- [Priss] At that son of a bitch, Mason, that's who!
- Huh?
No way, that would be against Article 2
of the Knight Saber's Code.
You know that.
Hey, Priss.
Get me a soda out of the fridge, okay?
- What the hell am I?
(fridge door opening)
Here.
(grunting)
(fridge door closing)
- How rude!
If you toss 'em around like that,
you can't open 'em right away.
- [Priss] So get it yourself.
- [Linna] What's gotten into you?
When you're done with that,
sweep the apartment, okay?
- The price I pay.
- [Linna] What's with you?
When someone feeds you, you naturally owe them a favor.
(intense music)
- The technologically integrated economic city project,
which GENOM has been advancing for some time now,
has finally received governmental approval.
GENOM will acquire all of District 3,
and present it to the world
as the leading edge business community.
Also, District 12, who's restoration has been delayed,
will become a single lodge GENOM industrial area.
In summary, we will move ahead with Stage 1
of the development of these two districts.
- The inhabitants of District 3 are most upset
about the lack of law and order,
so it should be only a matter of time
before they decide to sell their land.
- My hopes are riding on you, Mason.
Another failure would be distressing.
You had best not disappoint me.
- Yes, sir.
I completely understand, sir.
(machines whirring)
- [Priss] Happy birthday, Sho!
- Thanks!
- Okay, now blow out all the candles.
(blowing)
How old is he?
- 10 years old.
- 10 years old?
- Come on, let's eat.
Hey Priss, this is mama's own pizza,
and it really tastes great.
- Okay, here I go.
Yummy!
- Told ya!
- [Sho's Mom] Mind your manners!
We're in the middle of dinner.
- Oh, this isn't a dinner.
It's a party.
Right, Sho?
- Yeah, it's a party.
- It's wonderful to have Priss come over here.
Isn't it, Sho?
- I'm sorry to have you cut off so rudely.
- Oh, not at all.
When I'm at work, he's all alone.
I hate to think of him being that way.
Your looking out for him every now and then
is such a big help.
- I guess I'm just a really big hit with kids his age.
- I lost my husband, my home,
everything to the big earthquake seven years ago.
After that, we came to live here.
(game beeping)
But for Sho's sake, I've done what I can.
- [Priss] But it must be hard, always working so late.
- [Sho's Mom] I imagine it's the same for you.
- Well, in my case, it's more like a hobby.
- Well, I've just recently been able
to start saving some money.
Someday, I plan to live out in the country
where the air is clean.
But for now, it's just a dream.
(gentle music)
- [Priss] A dream.
(clinking)
(door closes)
(voices chattering)
(footsteps)
(intense music)
(electronic beeping)
- [Mason Voiceover] Sylia Stringray.
- Sis?
Hey sis, I'm coming in.
I'm done with the sales report.
Oh.
She must be in the data bank room.
And here I was, thinking I could catch her in her underwear.
(suspenseful techno music)
(water running)
(footsteps)
(yawning)
- Mason.
What's going on?
- Priss, they threw us all out.
We're gonna be evicted.
You've got to do something.
- I'll take care of this.
- GENOM Real Estate purchased this land from the government.
You're all trespassers.
So, you have no right to be here.
- You can't be serious.
(thudding)
- Wouldn't try that.
- Shut up!
- You're killin' me.
- Oh, come on, it's too early in the morning
to be having a riot.
What the?
Hey, hey, that's a little rough, isn't it?
Let her go.
You live around here?
How about I stop by your place later on, huh?
- Are you out of your mind?
I'm being evicted!
Now, do something about these bastards.
- I'm afraid what they're doing is completely legal.
(grunting)
- [Priss Voiceover] Shit.
You son of a bitch!
(grunting)
- It's a Boomer!
(gun banging)
- [Mason] That's enough.
(thudding)
(gasping)
- One of these days,
I'll uncover the truth about you.
- Be careful what you say, little puppy.
- Even a little puppy
can nibble a sleazebag like you to death.
(gasping)
(machines whirring)
(machine revving)
(creaking)
- Our home!
- Sho!
Stay back!
(rumbling)
(glass shattering)
- [Sho] Stop!
There's someone in there!
(dramatic techno music)
(thudding)
- [Sho's Mom Voiceover] Someday, I plan to live out
in the country, where the air is clean.
But for now, it's just a dream.
- Let's go.
- An eye for an eye.
- [Sylia] No operating on your own.
- [Priss] Sylia!
- Personal vengeance is a violation of Article 2.
- Solo actions are a no no.
Article 3 consent a full membership is required.
- So, what's with the suits?
- [Linna] Nene gaves us the information
as it came into AD Police,
including word about a boy who'd lost his mother.
- We're doing this preserve the Knight Sabers organization,
not just for you.
- Sylia.
(energetic techno music)
(engine revving)
♪ Sins are playin' on the faces of angels ♪
♪ Who are cornered in the dark and desperate night ♪
♪ Everyone rise within the grip of the night ♪
(engine revving)
♪ While knowing that something isn't right ♪
♪ I can't believe that there's going to be a fight ♪
♪ Oh, I know I would enjoy
(bike revving)
♪ I would be happy just to call it a night ♪
♪ But in my heart I know I cannot hesitate ♪
♪ Oh, you can't hide your eyes
♪ In there, truth never lies
♪ When the cards are stacked against you ♪
♪ When you wanna just lay down and die ♪
♪ You can turn it into courage now ♪
♪ And blow lower
♪ Never sink in, never again
♪ Nothing can stop you
♪ You're gonna win
♪ Never say give it up
♪ Never again
♪ Wanted tomorrow, fight
(electronic beeping)
♪ In the calm of love
(guns banging)
(exploding)
- [Pilot] This is Chopper Four.
I've just spotted a firefight on the GENOM building
about 840 feet up.
Benders look like BU-12B.
Attackers seem to be wearing hard suits.
(bike revving)
♪ Just as pure as a night
♪ Oh, I wonder when will fate come ♪
(guns banging)
(lasers blasting) (exploding)
- [Man] Chopper Four, come in.
Chopper Four--
- That does it!
My unit, move out now!
♪ Whether we may lose or win
♪ So now, that kind of heart
♪ 'Cause you can make them start ♪
(bike revving)
♪ You can turn it all to courage now ♪
♪ And look
(laser blasting)
♪ Never say give it up
♪ Every day
♪ Nothing can stop you
♪ You're gonna win
♪ Never say give it up
♪ Never again
♪ Run till tomorrow
♪ Fly till the end
(police sirens wailing)
♪ If you believe
♪ In the power of love
- [Mason] At last, welcome, Knight Sabers.
I have longed for this moment.
- [Sylia] This is the end of your ambitions, Mr.Mason.
You look as if you've resigned yourself to that.
- What you see is the look of the victor.
We stand here on the heights of GENOM, the summit of power.
Here, where I will reign.
Here, where you will die.
(metallic footsteps)
(lasers blasting)
(grunting)
(Nene screaming)
- [Nene] Ow!
(grunting)
(guns banging)
(yelling)
(intense music)
(whirring)
(gun banging)
- [Priss] Son of a, now what do I do?
You could have at least given me the instructions.
♪ You're not the only one
♪ Who's lonely in the night
(lasers blasting)
(whirring)
♪ The dreams we held on to as children ♪
♪ Still shine bright
♪ Like shooting stars
(gun banging)
(exploding)
♪ The pain and the sorrow
♪ Have no hold on tomorrow
♪ You can't give up
♪ It's time to fly
♪ Right on
(electronic beeping)
♪ And you can kiss me
Eat this!
(lasers blasting)
♪ A lot of people say I'm stormy weather ♪
Yes!
Okay, who's next?
♪ Break down the walls of deceits ♪
(exploding)
(engine revving)
♪ You and I were meant to be together ♪
♪ Forever more
(electronic beeping)
(laser blasting)
(suspenseful music)
(whirring)
- Sylia.
I knew it.
(whirring)
(sputtering)
- [Priss] Sylia.
(creaking)
(thudding)
(police sirens wailing)
(engines revving)
(footsteps)
(somber rock music)
♪ When rumors found you
♪ Remember you've got a friend
♪ Someone always waiting here for you ♪
♪ Nothing could change the way I feel for you ♪
♪ The smiles that you give me
♪ They show me the ecstasy
♪ They're locked in my heart as treasures ♪
♪ They'll keep me warm now and forever ♪
♪ Through tear stained eyes
♪ We search the skies
♪ Stars in heaven
♪ Whisper the story of how you and I ♪
♪ This love will never die
♪ Safe in my arms as long as you remember ♪
♪ Don't stop baby, dreamin'
♪ Don't stop baby, lovin'
♪ Don't stop baby, leavin'
♪ Promise to remember
♪ Don't stop baby, dreamin'
♪ Don't stop baby, lovin'
♪ Don't stop baby, leavin'
♪ I will always be here just for you ♪
♪ Even though we're not
♪ My love waits for me
♪ When gloominess finds you
♪ Remember you've got a friend
♪ Someone always waiting here for you ♪
♪ Nothing could change the way I feel for you ♪
♪ The smiles that you give me
♪ They show me the ecstasy