(door creaks open)
(footsteps)
(car door closes)
(engine starts)
(dramatic music)
- [Voice On Radio] That black car is at it again.
Heading west on Bayshore number three near Heneda.
All units in the vicinity, respond at once.
Don't lose him this time.
- [Leon] Hey David, what did he mean by that black car?
- You mean you didn't hear about it at today's meeting?
- Nah, I was asleep.
- [David] There's a rebuilt Griffon popping up
around here at night.
He keeps trashing outriders, but no fatalities yet
so it's being treated as horseplay
that's gotten out of hand.
The highway patrol can't cope.
- Ha, so someone's actually driving
one of those antique Griffons.
- Huh?
Oh look at that one go, it looks pretty souped up.
- Yeah, I know.
- What?
- She's my singing sweetheart.
- [Voice On Radio] Calling all AD police units,
TH video requests assistance.
Respond if you're nearby.
- Man, what a bunch of old ladies.
(sirens)
♪ I just can't love wholeheartedly ♪
♪ Do it blame it on this lonely crazy town ♪
♪ Burning highway
♪ Tonight I hear the--
- Band sounds as good as ever.
Huh? This engine's a gas guzzler.
- [Radio DJ] We have another accident report this morning.
Let's get the details from Mr. Drinkwater in the newsroom.
- [Mr. Drinkwater] Outrider casualties are mounting
and there's something very unusual about the situation.
- Hey, did you spend all night on that?
You really work hard.
Doesn't Celia worry about you?
- I'm too old for that.
- [Priss] Oh no you're not.
Where's pops?
- If you mean Dr. Raven, I think he's in the back.
- Pops, yo pops, it's me, Priss, fill 'er up.
- Call me Doctor.
How many times do I have to tell you?
Call me Doctor!
- Oh, there you are, pops.
Give me a tank full of Raven special.
- (groans) Doctor!
- Oh what a beaut.
What's she got?
- It's a twin turbo 1500, so about 700 horsepower.
- Whoa.
- The drive train works with a shaft
that doesn't use viscous oil.
That way there's little lag time or loss.
The instrumentation comes from combat hardware,
the new HS-130 to be exact.
There was one buried in the junkyard out back.
Can you believe that?
- You've really put something incredible together here.
Let me ride her.
- Huh?
- She's all finished, right?
So start her up.
- But it's just something I've put together for fun.
It's not something you can really ride--
- Be a good boy, Mackie, and do what I tell you to do, okay?
- Okay.
(engine revs)
(screaming)
- Damn it!
- Strike one.
- [Priss] I swear, this bike shouldn't guzzle gas
like it does.
- [Doctor] Can't be helped.
To get the power output you ordered, it has to.
- Hey pops.
- [Doctor] Yeah.
- Who's in this picture, pops?
- [Doctor] Doctor.
- Huh?
- I told you to call me Doctor.
- Alright, okay.
Okay, thanks a lot pops.
- [Both] Doctor!
(children playing)
(groaning)
(engines revving)
(dramatic music) (screaming)
(upbeat music)
(gunshots)
(groans)
- Alright, that's far enough.
Thank you very much.
(gunshots)
I planted an anti-personnel mod.
Lift your foot, and it goes off.
- Great, we lost again?
- Leave it to Celia to sacrifice Nene.
- [Woman] Come on, a bet's a bet.
Linna, do you mind?
- If we're paying for this, I'm gonna get my money's worth.
Come on, eat.
- So anyway, suddenly the jobs have stopped coming,
haven't they?
- Precisely.
- Well, no jobs for us, you know what that means.
- Peace on earth, huh?
Yeah, right.
- But no work is no good you know,
I wanna buy new clothes and trade in my old car.
- On the other hand, it's nice to be able to make time
to see your boyfriend, right?
- What's that?
You've got a boyfriend?
- Who do you mean?
Oh, that guy's already ancient history.
- How depressing.
- Uh, someday I'll be a 3D artist.
Who cares about art?
He was always talking about his dreams.
It's like he had no sense of reality.
- Well if you ask me, that was a waste Linna.
Oh, if it were me, even if we were poor,
so long as we both loved each other.
I'd want to be with him forever.
Oh I want a passionate love too and soon!
- Oh give me a break, you and your dreams.
You have no sense of reality.
- Ooh, you're so mean!
(laughter)
What is so funny?
You're always making fun of me!
I could get myself a man if I wanted to,
anytime I felt like it!
(drill whirs)
- Hmm.
(engine starts)
(backfires)
(sighs)
(laughs)
(explosion)
(brakes screeching)
- I'm already broke this month and then this sets me back.
This is not funny.
Just thinking about it pisses me off, man.
Things couldn't get any worse.
Asshole!
Hey, you alright?
Real funny, you son of a bitch.
Just you wait!
(alarms sound)
(groaning)
- Linna, the waist on this skirt you lent me is too big.
- What? No way!
What's your size?
- Uh, what's yours?
- That is none of your business.
(giggles)
Hey come on, quit dragging your feet.
- This is so stupid.
I don't need to have a doctor examine me.
- Considering all the stupid things you do,
you most certainly do.
You're gonna have a complete checkup
and get all your old injuries fixed.
Let's see.
Surgery is the blue line.
- Which way?
- [Linna] Come on, come on.
I told you, the blue line.
- Slow down, will you?
I'm a casualty.
Ow, look where you're going.
- [Linna] Look, look, that one's not too bad.
- So what? He's got a girl.
Man, is that an obnoxious crew.
- Not like you at all.
(engines roaring)
(screaming)
- [Nene] What?
You should do that stuff at Celia's place.
You can access computers anywhere in the world from there.
- [Priss] No can do.
Celia won't let me use her system for personal business.
- [Nene] Same here.
What do you think would happen if somebody caught us?
- [Priss] It'll be all right, I tell you.
It will only take a moment, now get a move on.
- [Nene] Oh it's always something like this with you.
You can pay me back by taking me out to eat.
- [Priss] Girl, all you think about is eating.
- [Nene] Okay, here's a list
of Griffons registered in Tokyo.
The model all but disappeared five or six years ago.
Presently, there are, let's see, four left.
All the owners are pretty ancient.
Hey, look at this guy!
He's 74 years old, I wonder if he's even capable of driving.
- Hmm, an aging bunch of collectors, huh?
Well it was an import aimed at enthusiasts.
Think you can bring up the list from three years back?
- Sure, just a sec.
We're up two, to a total of six.
- [Priss] Okay, get me the full rundown on those two.
- [Nene] Okay.
This one changed hands two years ago.
The current owner is J.B. Gibson, age 28.
He had an accident six months ago
and the registration was purged this past spring
after it expired.
- What can you tell me about that accident?
- Hmm, let me see.
What the?
There's a protection block on this level.
Oh hold on, I know.
I've got the chief's voice on disc.
- [Chief Toto] Chief Toto.
- [Nene] There, now we're clear for level four.
- Damn, you're good.
A passenger vehicle driven by J.B. Gibson
was waylayed on the lower deck of highway three
by the outrider gang and collided with the guard rail.
He was seriously assaulted,
suffered five compound fractures.
His passenger, Naomi Anderson, was also hospitalized,
suffering from extreme shock.
Hmm, J.B. Gibson.
- Hey, who the hell's in here?
- (gasps) Get down!
- Oh, it's you Nene.
What are you doing?
- Oh, just running an inquiry into the data
on the McPherson case.
- So are you free after work?
- Oh, my mom will get mad if I don't go straight home.
Ciao!
- Well, say hi to mom for me.
- Hi.
I was beginning to think I'd been abandoned.
- You can't just sit in front of a police station
forever, you know.
I ended up circling the AD police complex seven times.
- Oops, sorry.
- Your chariot awaits.
Where to now m'lady?
- I want a beer and a burger, now.
(grinding)
- It's my last request.
Doc, you have to give me the MFS control unit
or I'll never be able to fully use the car.
- [Doctor] You fool, what are you talking about?
If I'd known what you were going to do,
I'd never have built the thing.
It's not that I don't understand how you feel
but that's all in the past now.
Forget it and think of the future.
Make Naomi happy!
- Don't talk to me about Naomi!
- Gibson.
(engine revs)
- So, who's Mr. Sunshine?
(gunshots)
- Cut that out or take it someplace else, asshole!
(creepy music)
(explosion)
- Yo!
- Hello?
- Hey there, pops.
- If it's the bike you want, it's in the back.
Don't do anything reckless.
Lives and motorcycles don't last forever, you know.
- Yeah, sure.
What the?
- Hey, it's those two.
- I thought they looked suspicious
when we saw them at the hospital.
- [Doctor] Hospital you say?
- Yes, that woman was in a wheelchair.
- Yeah and she freaked out at the sound of motorcycles.
- She was out of her mind.
- [Doctor] So that's what Gibson meant, damn it.
- Gibson!
You know him?
- Well, kind of.
(phone rings)
- Hello Ravens, Doctor speaking.
Hello? Gibson?
Gibson, it's you, isn't it Gibson?
Answer me, Gibson!
Gibson, answer me.
- Pops.
- [Doctor] Where are you, you idiot?
I heard about Naomi, now don't do anything stupid.
Priss, uh, I mean...
I have a request to make of the Night Sabers.
Stop that fool Gibson.
- The Griffon, right?
- [Doctor] How did you know?
- So I'm right.
- Gibson!
J.B. Gibson!
(gunshots)
Hold it!
(engine starts)
(tires screech)
(gunshots)
- Anyway, he'll be a disaster unless we save them.
Celia, are you listening to me?
- I've got it.
So what about our fee?
- No problem, no problem.
Pops says he'll upgrade our motoroids for free.
- Hey, what are you talking about?
I didn't say word one about any such thing.
- Big deal, for you that's cheap.
- Well okay.
We can hardly refuse a request from Doctor Raven.
(exciting music)
- [Voice On Radio] This is Adam 13.
We have made contact with the Griffon.
He's on SK Avenue heading toward Takaito.
Requesting immediate assistance.
- Out of my way, move it you fool!
- [Voice On Radio] Calling all highway patrol units,
we have requested AD police assistance.
They have established a roadblock on Bayshore one.
Chase the bastard to them, do whatever it takes.
- [Linna] What kind of motorcycle is that?
- Mackie built it.
It's the only thing we've got that can catch the Griffon.
- Where's Nene?
- She'll be at AD police headquarters,
updating us on the situation.
Alright, let's go.
(sirens) (exciting music)
(explosion)
- Do you read me?
Listen, the Griffon's on the upper deck of highway four.
AD police is ready and waiting.
They set a trap on eastbound Bayshore one.
They're gonna chase him down the loop
of highway number nine.
- [Linna] Got it, thanks.
You heard her, Priss, Gibson's a goner
unless we stop him before he hits the Bayshore.
- [Priss] Okay, okay.
Let's do it.
- [Leon] Getting this hunk of scrap up here
must have really took some doing, huh?
- [David] Yeah, nobody's gonna just waltz up here
and punch through armor like this.
- No way.
Tonight's the end of the road for that bastard.
- [Voice On Radio] Report from Adam 12,
the Griffon has slipped into the loop
and is now on highway number nine.
- [Gibson] Nao, are you alright?
- Where are we?
Gib, what's going on?
- Naomi, are you--
- [Naomi] What have you done to yourself, Gib?
What have you done to this car?
- Nao, you're all right.
- Nevermind, just stop the car!
(screaming)
Gib!
- [Voice On Radio] Griffon sighted.
Something seems peculiar, I'm going to get closer.
Presently, 11 kilometers from the barricade.
ETA 142 seconds.
Transmitting visuals.
- Huh? The Night Sabers.
- Please Gib, please, wake up.
Don't die!
- [Man In Helicopter] I can't keep up.
This damn thing's just too fast.
- [Priss] This shit just gets worse.
Watch this.
Haul ass, go!
- [Mackie] Priss is taking some decent shortcuts,
but I don't know if she can catch up with him.
♪ Everyone is powerless to break the spell ♪
♪ Every ninja knocks you to your death ♪
- Damn it!
Crashed it again.
♪ Cuts through the night
♪ And the earth is trembling under my feet ♪
♪ If you can feel it too
♪ There's only one thing you can do ♪
♪ Open your windows now
♪ Close your eyes and be free
- Oops, excuse me.
- Who are you? What the?
♪ Shout it out until you can see the bright lights ♪
(explosion)
- We're bailing out.
I'm standing on the brakes but it won't stop in time.
- [Men] It's coming!
- [Celia] Priss, when I give the word, jump off the Griffon.
- [Priss] Celia, what the hell are you talking about?
I can't even see you.
- [Linna] It's okay, we're right behind you.
- [Celia] Now!
- [Priss] What kept you?
♪ Hold on tight
♪ Everything will be all right
♪ Just walk right out the door
♪ Don't be afraid of the night
♪ Scream love to someone you meet on your way ♪
♪ Make tomorrow a happier day
♪ Swear peace to someone that peace always stayed ♪
♪ Have courage come what may
(guitar music)
(screeching tires)
- Shoot the engine, you idiots.
(gunshots)
(explosion)
- Hey Leon, the Griffon, you suppose that like its creator,
it too became obsessed with revenge?
(sirens)
- [Nene] So, what finally happened to those two?
- Not much of anything happened to them.
They just got arrested.
Besides, you should know that better than any of us.
- It was under the THB's jurisdiction,
but I can't help admiring what they did.
- You know, I just can't really understand
that sort of thing.
- It's obvious.
People like Gibson and Naomi are victimized
because the authorities ignore the outriders
instead of catching them.
- Oh, you're always analyzing everything.
- By the way, where's Priss?
- She's doing a little work for me.
- Oof, I give up!
There's no way I can fix it.
- Hey, you're responsible for it.
- Mackie doesn't have to know.
Could you fix it for me, Doctor?
- [Doctor] Pops is okay.
- Thanks, Doc.
♪ They say when you fall in love ♪
♪ You'll find loneliness
♪ Every time the sun goes down
♪ You know it's not like me
♪ To let love
♪ Make me weak just 'cause you're not around ♪
♪ Alone in the twilight
♪ Always wandering on these empty streets ♪
♪ Rain has stopped falling now
♪ The pavement glimmers at me
♪ I've hurt for some time now
♪ Since you showed me how love can really feel ♪
♪ Tears keep falling at my feet ♪
♪ My wounded heart is revealed
♪ Every time we meet we start to fight ♪
♪ Can't we have just one romantic night ♪
♪ It starts when I'm feeling blue ♪
♪ That's when I always fix my sights on you ♪
♪ They say when you fall in love ♪
♪ You'll find loneliness
♪ Every time the sun goes down
♪ You know it's not like me
♪ To let love
♪ Make me weak just 'cause you're not around ♪
♪ I'm feeling so hopeless
♪ Always knowing my wish cannot come true ♪
♪ I'll never know the gentleness ♪
♪ That I had loving you
♪ Even though I say I've had enough ♪
♪ Try to hide the pain by acting tough ♪
♪ It starts when I'm feeling blue ♪
♪ That's when I always fix my sights on you ♪
♪ They say when you fall in love ♪
♪ You'll find loneliness
♪ Every time the sun goes down
♪ You know it's not like me
♪ To let love
♪ Make me weak just 'cause you're not around ♪
♪ They say when you fall in love ♪
♪ You'll find loneliness
♪ Every time the sun goes down
♪ You know it's not like me
♪ To let love
♪ Make me weak just 'cause you're not around ♪
♪ They say when you fall in love ♪