(engines rumble)
(laser whines)
(explosion rumbles)
(engine rumbles)
(car whines)
- [Man] This is Unit 303.
They appear to be heading for the space port.
Call in Unit 401.
He's on patrol in the vicinity of Shaft G9.
- We'll box them in on the lighter highway.
(vehicles whine)
(vehicle whines) (high swoosh)
- Hang on, Anri.
Just a little bit longer and we'll be free.
- I'm sorry.
Now of all times.
- Once we get through here, we'll be at the space port.
You suppose Nam's taken care of her part?
- If all's gone according to plan she has.
We can't turn back now.
No matter what happens, now if we don't get
to the planet, we won't have any future.
- Yes, I can't stand this place any longer.
Faster, Meg, faster, hurry, come on,
come on, step on it.
- Right. - Huh.
(engines whine) (groans)
(grunts) (engines whine)
(explosion rumbles) (women scream)
(lasers whine) (explosion rumbles)
(alarm blares) (engines whines)
- Number three, watch your front!
(screams) (explosion rumbles)
(fire crackles) (engines whine)
- Shit! (console cracks)
This is unit 10, I've lost sight
of unit seven, last seen in shaft F3
heading toward Ward Six, request to release Dobermans.
Repeat, request to release Dobermans.
- 10/4. (machine whines)
(dramatic music) (metal whines)
(metallic whine)
(engines whine) - It's the exit, we made it!
(grunts) (alarm whine)
A Doberman!
It's not use, damn.
We'll never make it.
- Set the car for auto cruise.
Meg, we'll just have to ditch on my signal.
Anri, you can do that, right?
- Yeah.
(machine beeps)
(engine whines) (Doberman growls)
(engine whines) (guns clack)
(guns ping) (guns whine)
(explosion rumbles) (dramatic music)
(Doberman whines) (machine clacks)
(Doberman growls)
(engines whine)
- What could be keeping Sylvia and the others?
They're late.
- Nam!
- I thought you were done for.
- Is she ready? - Yeah, come on.
Hurry, Sylvie, the patrols are starting
to make their rounds now.
- Hang on Anri, it's okay, hang on.
- [Lou] It's a Doberman!
(women scream) - Get on board, quickly!
That door won't hold for long.
- Meg, Lou, hurry up, come on, let's go!
(women scream)
(metal cracks)
- Go on! (guns whine)
(Doberman growls) (gun rocks)
(explosion rumbles) - Look out!
- Nam, what are you doing?
- There's no hope for me now, go on,
get out of here, hurry!
- No, no, I just can't abandon you all!
(guns whine) (guns rumble)
- What are you doing standing there,
move it, (grunts)
- Lou!
- Hang on, Lou.
(gun whines)
- Meg, Lou!
- Sylvie, get freedom, get enough,
enough freedom for all of us too.
(grunts) (machine whines)
- No! (guns rumble)
(sobs) (metal cracks)
(screen cracks)
(engines rumble) (explosion roars)
(engine whines)
(metal clacks)
(alarm whines) (groans)
(laser whines) (explosion rumbles)
(groans) (ship rumbles)
(engines whine) (Doberman growls)
(upbeat music)
♪ Alone in my heart
♪ I can't sleep at all
♪ My world fell apart
♪ My back to the wall
♪ Storm clouds are near
♪ Feeding on fear benign
♪ Downtown is washed
♪ In tranquil moonlight
♪ But out on the road
♪ It lurks in the night
♪ What cursed us before
♪ Has come back again
♪ Can't you feel it under your skin ♪
♪ When we're together there are no worries ♪
♪ You and I were meant to be side by side ♪
♪ My love for you is an endless story ♪
♪ I know what you need
♪ To be satisfied
♪ Don't close your heart
♪ You don't have to face the night alone ♪
(engine rumbles)
- [Leon] It's ridiculous, I tell ya.
We haven't had any sleep all night.
- Well, come back to my place later
and I'll make a new man out of you.
- Not now, I've got a headache.
- You always have a headache.
- We'll arrive at the scene shortly.
Fasten your seat belts. (groans)
- Can it, now go on and set us down.
Right smack in the middle of those bastards.
- [Pilot] Ah, yes sir.
- [Officer] Given the results of our analysis
of the debris, we think it's connected
with the SDCP people.
- This is more than I can put up with.
This is the last straw, this is just too much.
Don't they have any better ways
of throwing their trash away?
- So, what about the pilot?
- We're searching for him right now, sir,
but under the circumstances, we think
he's probably. - Yeah there's no way
anyone could have survived this.
(sirens whine) - Captain.
The results of our inquiry into the model
registration number we found earlier
confirms that it is Orca Four, a shuttle
belonging to SDCP, no comment regarding its occupants.
- [Officer] If we're dealing with SDCP, we might
as well pack it in now.
- So what we have is over our heads
in more ways than one. - No, I'm not
so sure about that. (engines rumble)
Well speak of the devil, here they come now.
- [Reporter] At least according
to available reports, therefore
the SDCP, the Space Development Corporation
is embarking on a full inquiry
into the situation at the gaint Genaros staytion
which is the supply center for the moon base.
According to the SDCP, repairs
are being made to Genaros as quikcly as possible.
Projected date of completeion has not
been announced yet, but coprorate director.
(dramatic music)
(breathes)
- [Quincy] Something will have to be done on your end
about this latest fiasco!
- I understand, I did not mean to cause
you any inconvenience, Mr. Flint.
- This has nothing to do with me or my people.
- [Kaufman] Yes sir, I am considering the worst
case scenario, rest assured.
- [Quincy] Do that!
- It would seem that at least for now,
Kaufman is following our orders.
- He better, however our top priority
is to find the D.D. which was supposed
to be on that shuttle.
If the AD police or the Tower become
aware of its existence, then we will
be forced to temporarily cut the strings
between us and our puppet, SDPC.
- Oh really?
On the other hand it might be more expedient
to cut some other strings, for example,
the ones that make you dance.
- The Tower and the AD police will be
investigating this, but I know what
those girls want which gives me the edge.
Even so, shielding you is risky, Largo
and should I fall, I will not fall alone.
Well?
(laughs)
- The majority of workers on Generos
are F and G series space development Booomer.
There's a strong possibility that effective unit
caused some sort of screw up in operations.
You go and listen to what their people
have to say and put it on the record
as a formality. - Just a formality?
- Listen to me, don't you dare go half-cocked
on this one, this is SDCP we're up against
which is directly controlled by the government.
I don't wanna make a big fuss only
to get the evil eye from upstairs, okay?
- The only thing you're concerned about
is your retirement, you chicken shit.
(growls)
- You try dealing with officers
like you who go wild every time there's
a big case, and see if you don't end up
like me, my head is on the chopping block.
All the time!
- Whoa (laughs)
You S.O.
(engines whine)
Don't get too caught up in the nightlife.
- [Daley] There's almost all Boomers on that station.
I'm not looking forward to this at all.
- [Leon] Yeah, I know.
- Anyway, rumor has it that illegal arms sales
are being routed through Genaros.
Quite a coincidence, eh?
My gut feeling tells me there's
some kind of connection, call it
feminine intuition. - Coming from you,
I believe it, here catch.
(dramatic music)
(machine growls)
♪ Tears no comfort
♪ For the hungry child
♪ Crying wakes the silence
♪ Of the night (grunts and groans)
♪ Gold and dreary path
♪ That leads to nowhere (machine growls)
♪ Can't see through the darkness ♪
♪ For the light (metal whines)
♪ Fallen angel here you are
- Are you turned on? ♪ Stay with a smile
(engines whine)
♪ In your hand
♪ Soldier girl, fighting to right the wrong ♪
♪ Passion red is a rose in your heart ♪
♪ Soldier girl, this is the way of love ♪
♪ Victory is all your dreaming of ♪
(engine whines)
- [Nene] Linna, have you heard about that girl, Sylvie?
- [Linna] Yeah I heard about her, she's the girl
Priss is hanging around with, right?
- [Nene] Yeah, she comes into town just
the other day and in no time she's
causing a sensation, she's so gorgeous.
- Oh that's just because everyone finds
a fresh face exotic, I mean, she can't
hold a candle to me, right (laughs).
- Hi.
- Priss, you are your usual terrific self tonight.
- Thanks, Nene.
- How about I quit my job at Phoebe's
and become your manager, if you wanna
sign with EMI now's the time.
- Oh there you go again.
Hey, Priss, did you know that Linna
says her latest boyfriend is one of EMI's directors?
- I don't wanna know, I've had it
with you crying your heart out.
- [Linna] Oh, you're mean, it's serious
this time, and I deserve happiness too you know.
- [Nene] Being happy with Linna, what an awful thought.
- [Priss] You got that right.
- Oh, you're both picking on me.
- You look like you're having fun, I hope
I'm not interrupting anything.
- You're late, Sylvie, I already
finished my last set.
- Oh.
I'm sorry, I had a little business.
Hey, these are your friends, right?
- Yeah, Nene and Linna.
- You're Sylvie right, Priss has been
telling us all about you, about what
a terrific biker you are and she's right
you're so beautiful, I bet you've got
tons of boyfriends. - You're too kind.
Pleased to meet you.
- [Linna] Same here.
- [Priss] Okay, now that we're all here,
how's about we get going?
- Right. - Speaking of which.
(balls clack)
- [Fargo] Sorry about this, Sylia.
- Okay same as ever, eh Fargo, why
don't you at least wear a nicer suit for once.
- Hey, I'm sorry, I've got all kinds
of expenses, you know, plus, with
the cost of living today, that sort
of thing is out of my reach anyway.
Did you have a look at the report I sent you?
- Kaufman at SDPC is in the hot seat again, right?
- [Fargo] You got it.
He's risen very far, very fast, but apparently
he fell in with a Genom splinter group.
Secretly developed a next generation super weapon
and shipped it to a space station
with the intention of selling it to
an unfriendly power.
- The D.D airborne battle mover, right Fargo?
I've heard about it here and there.
Is it already finished then?
- They have a prototype.
Now what Kaufman wants is either
its recovery or its destruction.
Also find his girlfriend.
Seems she turned out to be a thief.
No leads on her identity though.
- Meaning the Genom Tower is behind all of this?
- As a matter of fact, our beloved Genom corporation
has nothing to do with this incident, hm.
- This is a messy job and it's not
going to come cheap, Fargo.
- I've already deposited half the fee.
I'm sure you'll find it more than acceptable.
- Fargo, I'm just no match for you.
Okay, I'll contact you in the usual manner.
Till then. (door whines)
(engines roar)
(lights snack)
- I tell ya, I can't get used to this place
no matter how many times I come in here.
- Leon, I'll show you the deceased.
- Forget about the guy, what a waste
this happened to such a good-looking girl.
Right, Nene? - Oh, yes sir,
very good looking.
- Since that's neither here nor there
would you mind just shutting up
for a minute? - Mm.
(laughs)
- [Examiner] Now there are more bodies waiting,
I'll tell you what I figured out.
Write this down.
First the woman was with the man
the cause of death was massive blood loss.
The main external wounds are this injury
to the left side of the neck as well as.
- This is the eighth accident in
the last two weeks with the circumstances
all the same, previous reports indicate
hardly any blood stains at the scenes, too.
Wonder if it isn't a vampire after all.
The newspapers are causing an uproar
with their constant vampire headlines.
- That's what I like about this town,
it's never dull. - I bet that the vampire
uses some kind of modern vehicles.
Since they were all freeway incidents.
- [Leon] I don't know, could be a Boomer.
- Boomer, you mean Boomers can drink blood?
- They might if they were type 33-S
which had an artificial blood supply.
But fortunately, there aren't any
of those around nowadays, since it was
the one Boomer that was banned.
- Then it is a vampire after all.
- Well whichever it is, unless we bring it in soon,
there won't be any cute girls left.
- That's true, then I must be careful too.
(groans)
The investigation section is working
on the angle that the culprit the vampire
serial killings is a 33-S, but the production
data states that the 33-S were all eliminated.
Tell me, why was this Boomer banned?
- They were initially designed to be
Sexaroid toys but they were augmented
so they could synchronize to advanced weapons systems.
That caused problems.
- A Sexaroid (screams).
So do they really exist?
- I thought you weren't interested
in perverted things like that?
- Why not?
Hey, I wonder if they're as pretty
as this girl I met yesterday.
- Who? - Oh, this biker friend
of Priss's, her name is Sylvie
and she's really hot, oh with a body
that you could just die for, and Priss
gets along with her unusually well.
- I see, sounds like someone I'd like to meet.
All right inform me if anything else happens.
- Okay. (screen whines)
- [Internal Voice] A super weapon and a 33-S?
When will they learn, as you sow
so shall you reap, the question now is
what is his lady friend after?
(engines roar)
(car engine roars)
(machines rumble)
- [Priss] Here you go.
- Oh, thank you.
- So, how do you like this town so far?
(groans)
Oh, talk about mixed blessings.
That's the Genom Corporate Research Center.
They're the source of all the boomer trouble.
Scary.
(cat meows) Aw.
Here you go. (cat meows)
(cat meows) Uh-uh, the rest is mine.
(laughs) (cat meows)
- Here kitty kitty. (cat growls)
- Hey, are you okay? - Yeah.
- Doesn't like beautiful women.
Must be a female cat.
- Oh, Priss.
Even that cat is free.
(car engine roars)
Freer than me.
- Come on, let's go, I've got a rehearsal
at the club. - Oh, thanks, but I'm
gonna stay here a little longer.
- Hmm? - I'm free, I'm free now.
Free. - Free?
- Right. - I don't know
what you're talking about, but I'll catch you later.
Call me. (engine roars)
- I will.
(explosion rumbles) (liquid squelches)
(sirens blare)
- [Quincy] The question is how much will
the little bitch teach the D.D?
- You must strike now, before the 33-S
fully trains it, is there nay possibility
that she will be able to synchronize
with the D.D's J-1 unit?
- There's no telling.
As long as they are fully active, the possibility exists.
And though its maintenance free,
the 33-S is an old model, it won't
stand a chance in the city.
- Knowing this, she will logically seek
to obtain the 33-S design data disk.
- And this vampire business has the city
in an uproar, we can no longer leave this
in Kaufman's hands, recapture it all costs
before either AD police or the Tower
focus their attentions on us.
And when you find the 33-S.
(dramatic whine)
After all, a fall from this height
could be dangerous to my health.
(somber music)
(gasps)
- Don't do it anymore, it's too dangerous now.
If you're caught, you'll be eliminated.
You've already done enough for me.
You've gotta live for your own sake
from now on (sobs).
- That's not true, Anri.
Right now, this is the only way I have
of maintaining your systems, but,
I've finally pinpointed the location
of the data disk, once we have that,
we won't have to do this anymore.
Soon, yes, in just a little while
we'll be able to live completely
under our own power.
(metal clacks)
(machine clicks)
(dramatic music)
(door clicks)
(growls)
- Who the hell are you?
- Why, I'll leave that up to your imagination.
(machine whines) - 33-S?
Where are the guards?
(groans) (body thumps)
- Real cute.
Here it is.
(gasps)
Still around, huh?
That was careless of me.
- [Guard] If it isn't the current hot topic
of conversation, thrilled to meet you.
- Well then, I'd like to make you even happier.
Why don't you take off those tacky sunglasses?
- Like this? (growls)
(gun roars) (gun clicks)
(gasps)
(glass tinkles) (metallic swooshing)
(explosion rumbles) (engine roars)
(engines rumble)
(wood bangs) - Dammit, I'm surrounded
by brainless bastards, hey McLeod,
have you tracked down the identity
of yesterday's victim yet?
- Hey, Leon! - What the hell's wrong
with you morons. - Call, Daley on three!
- [Captain] What, Daley, how long is that slacker
gonna hang around up there?
Tell him to get his butt back in here!
- Leon, sounds like he's in a good mood.
- Eh, he's just his usual charming self.
So tell me what you found out.
- Finally chased down Kaufman.
He was planning to do an illicit deal
with the super weapons, in cahoots
with the head of the GPCC.
I also managed to get a technical readout
on the stolen device, it's packing
some serious firepower. - Just another battle mover.
I'll bring it in with an armored trooper.
Daley, don't worry, I can handle it.
- (laughs) Don't underestimate it, Leon.
It's a next generation battle mover,
equipped with a J-1 auto control system
and highly intelligent on board automation.
And to top it all off, those idiots
installed a nuclear dead man destruct device.
- Before you go off hunting that battle mover,
we need prior authorization, you screw up
and my ass gets fried too.
(wood bangs) - Good work, Daley.
Now get your butt back here while you still can.
(phone whines) - Where are you going?
- On patrol, if I meet the vampire,
I'll break its fangs and bring em back as souvenirs.
- Oh listen, Leon, the patrol choppers
are each carrying an armored trooper
so don't use em to go patrolling.
- [Leon] Right, and thanks.
- Are you sure this is all right Leon?
I need flight authorization for an
emergency take off. - Don't worry about it.
I'll take the responsibility.
- [Pilot] Yes, Sir.
(engines whine)
(engine roars) (dramatic music)
(lazers whine) (explosions rumble)
(explosions rumble) (lazers whine)
(explosion rumbles)
- Fire fight spotted on highway five,
headed north, north east.
- All right, circle around and pursue.
- Roger.
(explosions rumble) (lazers whine)
(explosion rumbles) (groans)
- Ah! (metallic thump)
(metallic swooshing) (engine roars)
(screams) (metallic swooshing)
(water sloshes)
- [Boomer] Feeling gutsy, Bit, the 33-S
is finally at the end of a rope.
- [Boomer] Yeah, let's finish her off fore the cops come
(rocks shatter)
(metal whines) (roars)
(gun roars) (explosion rumbles)
(grunts) (explosion whines)
- Ah! (bullets whir)
(explosion rumbles)
- [Pilot] Combat machine unrecorded in data bank.
Should I contact headquarters?
- Contact them if anything happens to me.
Do it.
(metal rumbles)
(grunts)
(metal thumps) Okay, hold it right there.
I'm not gonna do anything.
Just come outta there.
(machine whines)
- What's happening?
What?
(screams)
(metal clangs)
(metal snaps) (metal grunts)
(high whine) (metal growls)
(high swoosh) - What the hell?
(metal grunts) - Don't underestimate
it, Leon, it's a next generation
battle mover, equipped with a J-1
auto control system and highly intelligent
on-board automation, and to top it all off,
those idiots installed a nuclear dead man
destruct device. (metal whirs)
(grunts) (rock rumbles)
(grunts) (metal clangs)
(metal thumps) (electric crackles)
I'm not finished, not, not yet.
(metal whirs) Here we go.
(electric crackles) (groans)
(grunts) (electric crackles)
What? (metallic thump)
(grunts) Unless I put this thing
down quickly, the city'll go up in smoke.
I've got to.
(metal cracks) (groans)
(metal whines) (explosion rumbles)
Over there, is it?
(metallic thump)
- [Sylia] Knight Sabers, it's show time!
(guns whine) (guns whir)
- Now! (explosions rumble)
(grunts)
- What's going on?
Oh no, the computer's gone onto
full auto mode, it's decided that I'm dead.
All that's left now is.
- (grunts) Destroy it quickly.
It'll self destruct once it runs out of power.
We'll be blown to pieces along
with the entire city (grunts)
- [Priss] What is that, Nene?
- [Nene] Ah, right, he means it.
It's got a micro-neutron bomb and it's only
180 seconds away from critical mass.
- [All] What?
(metallic swooshing)
- Sylvie! (gasps)
- It's you, Priss.
Kill, kill me, the D.D has fused to me
and if you kill me it should shut down.
Hurry! - Why, why you, Sylvie?
- Please, it's completely out of control now.
If you leave me like this, I'll take
you and Anri with me.
- [Priss] I can't.
(metal whines)
- [Sylia] What's wrong with you, Priss, do it!
- No, I can't shoot her.
(metal thumps) (metal roars)
- [All] Priss!
(metal cracks) (explosion rumbles)
(metal thumps) (lazers roar)
(screams) (metal whines))
(metal cracks) (metal whirs)
(screams) - Stop it, stop it, stop it.
(screams) Stop it, D.D (screams).
(whines) (explosion rumbles)
(metal thumps)
- Priss.
- Here I come!
(guns whine) (explosions burst)
- [All] Priss!
- Priss.
(gasps) - Sylvie!
(lazer whines) - Priss.
- Sylvie! (somber music)
Sylvie, I can't believe it's you.
- Priss, take this, there's a girl, Anri
waiting back in my apartment.
Please, give it to her, without it,
she'll become like me, forced to hurt people.
I beg you.
- Why'd you do it?
- I want to be free, like you, free.
- Sylvie?
Sylvie (sobs).
Oh, god.
- I understand the situation.
Priss, do you think you should hand over that data?
- I know, but Sylvie was a friend.
I can't betray my friends.
- All right then, but you must go soon.
The rest of us will disperse now.
(water plinks) (rain patters)
(thunder cracks) (lightning crackles)
- [Largo] Sylia.
Sylia Stingray.
(thunder cracks)
(dramatic music)
♪ If you look in her heart
♪ Into anyone's heart
♪ Tell me whose would it be
♪ Oh can't you see
♪ That I want to be
♪ Your only one
♪ If I could go back in time
♪ And I could look in your mind ♪
♪ Tell me what would I see
♪ What did you feel
♪ Could love be real
♪ Might we too be together
♪ Oh I hate to see the sun go down ♪
♪ Lonely twilight leaves me crying ♪
♪ Still I know somehow
♪ I won't forget your smile
♪ Your eyes tell me I am the one ♪
♪ You told me all the secrets
♪ In your heart
♪ I won't forget your kiss
♪ Your tender lips whisper to me ♪
♪ This world's an empty place
♪ And no one should spend their life alone ♪
♪ I remember your eyes
♪ And recall sunny skies
♪ But my tears fall like rain
♪ Washing away
♪ Sweet yesterdays tender moments together ♪
♪ Oh I hate to see the sun go down ♪
♪ Lonely twilight leaves me crying ♪
♪ Still I know somehow
♪ I won't forget your smile
♪ Your eyes tell me I am the one ♪
♪ You told me all the secrets
♪ In your heart
♪ I won't forget your kiss
♪ Your tender lips whisper to me ♪
♪ This world's an empty place
♪ And no