(dramatic music)
- Thanks for waiting, bringing hot new discs to you.
It's time for today's spotlight corner.
Every week we bring you the most
kick ass cuts in the universe.
Today we introduce a new record by Vision and her band,
The Revengers, who are back on the scene
breaking a year long silence.
It's rocketing up the charts faster
than mercury in midsummer.
I'm telling you this one is hot.
It's the one you've been waiting for.
It's our pick for today so, let's hit it.
Here's Vision and the Revengers hot new disk,
the most baboo cut in the universe.
Say yes, let's go!
(\"Say Yes\")
♪ Like the wind
♪ You have come and gone
♪ This broken heart
♪ Will somehow carry on
♪ Not even death could take your love away ♪
♪ I still recall
♪ The words you said to me
♪ I'll be strong
♪ Won't give up easily
♪ But they're just whispers on the rising wind ♪
♪ For I keep running
♪ I always feel the world is fall down around me ♪
♪ Still I keep running
♪ With every step I take I can hear you calling ♪
♪ Keep on moving til the storm is gone forever ♪
♪ Say yes, the fire's so much hotter than yesterday ♪
♪ Keep burning
♪ Say yes, helplessly I know the pain ♪
♪ But I was lost and lonely
♪ Say yes, there's got to be a sign ♪
♪ You can send my way
♪ Hear me say I can be, I can do ♪
♪ I can sing, I can live
♪ Behind the walls
♪ But shining through the pain
♪ And it hurts
♪ Right through the driving rain ♪
♪ The cold steel blade splits the darkness ♪
♪ And the light
♪ Will not capture me
♪ Because your dreams have finally set me free ♪
♪ I'll hold them in my heart forever ♪
♪ When I look up now
♪ It's hard to see through all the tears ♪
♪ That I've been crying
♪ Still I look up now
♪ Knowing that your love is waiting for me ♪
♪ Stars up in the night bring hopes of new tomorrows ♪
♪ Say yes, the fires so much hotter that yesterday ♪
♪ Keep burning
♪ Say yes, helplessly I know the pain ♪
♪ When I was lost and lonely
♪ Say yes, there's got to be a sign ♪
♪ You can send my way
♪ Hear me say I can be, I can do, ♪
♪ I can sing, I can live
- Mr. Chairman, Genom and Gulf and Bradley
will each investigate 50% of the capital,
and the patents will all be
the joint property of both parties.
- This contract appears to be in order.
Continue, Mr. Yamada.
- As regards to the joint development,
Gulf and Bradley's development department
will have charge of the endoskeleton
and the mode of power systems.
And Genom will have charge of the defensive armor
and the offensive weapons systems.
Of course, the ultimate head of development
will be your own Dr. McLaren.
- Well, Doctor?
- Gentlemen, the research facilities
have already been completed.
If you will please observe.
We have assembled the very best
of Genom's scientific know-how.
The laboratory can be up and operational in one month.
- That's just fine, Mr. Yamada.
We have absolutely no objection.
- Thank you, sir.
We eagerly await your arrival in Japan, Doctor.
- I'm looking forward to it too,
so I can meet some beautiful geisha girls.
(chuckling loudly)
- Mr. Yamada, is he by any chance?
- Yes, sir, the Model 55-C boomer
is Genom's bestselling product.
- Our new modals should do even better once its finished.
(water splashing)
Give my regards to Mr. Quincy.
(electricity buzzing)
- What?
(dramatic music)
- Go.
(gun firing)
(gasps deeply)
(men gasping deeply)
(deep gasping)
(heavy breathing)
- What the?
Oh, hell!
Help!
- Chopper three here.
Incident at the Gulf and Bradley building.
Emergency dispatch.
- Oh, god.
(tires screeching)
(guns firing)
(helicopter blades roaring)
(emergency siren blaring)
- [Officer] Let's see him through.
- Where is the assailant?
- It appears to have fled to the river.
We've extended the dragnet out to 20 miles.
- That's thinning it out, but we've got no choice.
What does our survivor have to say?
- He says he couldn't see the attacker's face at all.
Also, he has no idea who it could've been.
- Probably because there are too many possibilities.
- Huh?
- The victim was a chairman of a major concern.
There'd be as many people with scores to settle
as there are stars in the sky.
- [Detective] Then the other victims were just collateral?
- [Captain] Could be.
(plane engine roaring)
- [Kou] How about this, Madam?
- Thank you.
- Tokyo is only 30 minutes away.
- Oh.
- Is something worrying you?
- I'm scared, Kou.
I'm not afraid that I might die,
but I'm terrified of what I'm trying to do now.
- We can still turn back.
- Uh-uh, I decided on this myself.
I don't intend to turn back.
I don't intend to quit, but.
(plane engine roaring)
- Miss Vision, could you tell us
about your first impressions of Tokyo?
- I'm not really sure.
I just got here yesterday.
(reporters laughing)
I'll be able to give a more meaningful answer
when I finish this tour.
- Why did you come here a whole week before your concert?
- Because there are several places I want to visit.
- Miss Vision, may I inquire as to why
you've suddenly gone back on live tour?
- Because I want to present new emotions with my music.
- New emotions, ma'am?
- Yes, I want to sing about all kinds of human emotion,
laughter, despair, joy, grief, regret,
anger, malice all types of emotions.
- Word is that after her press conference,
Miss Vision disappeared as usual.
Let's switch briefly to Mrs. Nakamura in Shibuya.
Miss Nakamura? - Hi, this is Nakamura.
Will you take a look at this line?
Isn't it incredible?
It's made up of Vision's fans who are all here
to buy advanced tickets for her concert.
Some of them have been here all night.
Excuse me, Miss, how long have you been in this line?
- Since 3:00 a.m.
- Do you like Vision?
- Oh, you bet.
I've got all her CDs and LDs starting with her debut.
I'm a big, big, big, big fan.
- Give me a break.
You only buy them because she's popular.
- You don't like her?
- It's not her singing.
It's her marketing technique that gets me.
She's nothing more than a question mark.
Who's she supposed to be Batman?
- [Nene] Kind of takes after you, doesn't she, Priss.
- [Priss] Is that so?
- Earth to Linna are you with us?
- I feel like I've met this singer Vision somewhere before.
- No way, it must have been someone
who was just trying to look like her.
(boat whistle blowing)
(machine whirring)
- How much longer, Shin?
- Two more hours.
- We move out at midnight,
and listen if anything goes wrong,
put Miss Reika's personal safety first and act accordingly.
Protect her with your lives.
Don't worry about me at all.
(gentle music)
- Dear, Reika, how are you?
I think, I mentioned my engagement in my last letter.
Well, the top news this time is this.
He gave it to me.
Pretty nice design, don't you think?
I told him about you.
He says he'd really like to meet you.
Well, in other news.
Some friends through a bachelorette party for me.
Here are some snapshots.
Everyone picked on me,
and I got teased a lot.
But it was really a fun party.
It looks like we'll be postponing the wedding date.
But I'll let you know as soon as it's set,
so please attend even if you have to break a concert date.
I'm hoping grandfather, Kou, and all the rest will come too.
Well, that's all for now.
Goodbye, Sis, I love you.
(gun cocking)
(gasps deeply)
- You took three seconds, Madam.
In a real situation that would've been enough to kill you.
Well, first of all, not noticing my footsteps
showed a lack of attention.
- [Reika] Kou, if you were to give me a score for this,
what would it be, say 50 out of a possible hundred?
- [Kou] About a 20, I think.
(engine revving)
(dramatic music)
(yawns deeply)
- [Scientist] Dr. McLaren,
the rate of epidermal cell adhesion is tapering off.
- It's a sign that it's nearly complete.
Damn shame.
Looking at it makes me think that strength
and ugliness must go hand in hand.
- A regular modern day Frankenstein's monster, huh?
(alert beeping)
(suspenseful music)
- Emergency in Block 24!
All personnel evacuate the area.
- The outer wall is too think.
We'll use one of the walk ways to get in.
- Roger.
- The intruder is heading for walkway number two.
- Someone's in the walkway.
- Shoot could get him. - No.
- Miss Reika. - No, Kou.
I can't shoot him.
- I've seen enough.
Damage? - Nine boomers
and four areas of structural damage.
Fortunately, no serious injuries.
Test models also undamaged.
Intruder has escaped and disappeared.
- [Quincy] Is this machine the same as the one in Houston?
- Absolutely.
Mr. Quincy, I'm returning to Texas.
The boomer is nearly complete.
I'm no longer needed here!
- No you won't.
You'll remain here until all the tests are completed.
I have a general idea who it was.
It must be the Chang group.
- [Man In Blue] You mean, Hou Bang?
Could they be after the new boomer?
- Probably.
Dr. McLaren, not to worry.
You are not the target.
Take some R and R for a week or so.
- Get a load of this.
There's nothing left.
- Looks like a ceramic blast proof overlay.
- Wait a minute please!
I can't let you in here!
- A.D. Police let me check around.
- I trust you have a search warrant.
Our company does have its secrets.
Entry into this section is forbidden to outside personnel.
- Hmm?
Well, all I can see is you look like
you're trying to hide something.
You know what I mean?
- What might that be?
- Something in violation of the law
like maybe a new type of boomer?
- You can't be serious.
May I remind you that we're the victims.
- Victims, huh?
- Put me down.
- Looks like a little overkill, don't you think?
(scientist groaning)
(carnival goers screaming)
- [Sylia] You think you're Harry Lime
choosing a place like this for a meeting.
- Just a little change of atmosphere, Sylia.
Besides we won't have to worry about eavesdroppers up here.
- So what's the job?
- Complete details are on the data disk.
I'll just hit the highlights.
An executive of a certain corporation
came to Japan at Genom's invitation.
The job is body guarding that bigwig.
- Body guarding someone associated with Genom?
That doesn't sit well with me.
- The fee is 50 million,
30 in advance,
20 on successful completion.
- Alright, I suppose.
- [Male] Now whoever is after him is extremely tough.
I hear they took out a boomer with one shot.
It may be a body guarding job.
But you'll be risking your life.
Please be as careful as you can.
Your body guarding must be in secret nothing overt.
This is an insist request of the client Mr. McLaren.
- Drop the investigation!
What the hell does that mean?
Just tell me why?
- Upstairs said I had to remove you.
I don't know anymore than that either.
- Genom's putting on the pressure again, huh?
Look, Chief, there's more to this
than just some terrorist attack.
We've gotta check out Genom.
- Here brought you something. - What's your problem?
- Tickets to the Vision concert!
- [Naoko] Right.
- Wow, front row seats.
- These were not easy to get.
- [Nene] Thank you.
- Look I'm not dropping this case, you got that!
(door slamming)
- Daley.
I hereby place Detectives Daley Wong
and Leon McNichol on two weeks paid leave.
They are absolutely forbidden to work,
investigatively or otherwise.
- Yes, sir, Chief.
- And try not to let that hothead boil over.
Just be careful.
(engine sputtering)
- Here we are.
- Huh?
- [Daley] It's big isn't it?
- [Leon] Even a low ball estimate of its cost
would be about 700 billion.
- What the hell is Genom planning to build here?
Their answer to Disneyland maybe?
- Well, I don't see Mickey Mouse anywhere.
(Daley chuckles)
Well, well, well.
- What do you see Snow White?
- [Leon] No, more like someone who'd make her
eat the poisoned happen.
Chairman Quincy himself has come out to see the job site.
- So where to now, Leon?
- The St. Regis Hotel.
- There go our paychecks.
- We're not gonna check in.
- Makes no difference.
Even a cup of coffee there cost two or 3,000.
(Priss sighing)
- This is a drag it's like being in a steam bath.
- We had to get a room from which
we could monitor the hotel, Priss.
It's just for a little longer.
- I know that.
It's just not easy sitting in a hot room
watching people lounge around a pool having drinks.
- Mm-hmm.
- [Priss] He's just a dirty old pervert.
Be careful he doesn't jump you, Nene.
- Here you go, sir, one Blue Hawaii.
- [McLaren] Arigato, Little Miss.
- [Priss] Sylia, I should've gotten
to infiltrate the hotel too.
- What's this, 5th floor, coffee shop, window seat?
- What is it?
Leon what's he doing here?
- There seems to be more to this job than meets the eye.
Things are getting interesting.
- You figure it out? - Yeah.
When our expert analyzed the photos,
he said the tower was a production factory,
and the city-like area was a mock battle stage.
- For boomers? - Yep.
A performance testing round.
- Things are getting interesting.
- Room service I've brought the champagne you ordered.
Good evening, sir.
- Yes, this is St. Regis Hotel room 2011.
No, not another blonde.
I think an Oriental this evening.
Make sure she's young.
- Yes, sir.
We'll send you an incomparable beauty.
Oh, about 17.
(machine beeping)
- Sylia, do you read me?
Looks like he's ordered up another call girl for tonight.
Nothing else to report.
- [Sylia] Roger continue surveillance.
- Okay.
- [Priss] After we went to all the trouble,
to buy off the hotel manager.
We should've put concealed cameras and microphones in there.
- We couldn't intrude on the client's privacy now, could we?
- But just having him wear a transmitter isn't good enough.
- Priss, I don't think the enemy wants to assassinate him.
- Huh?
- There were plenty of opportunities to kill McLaren
during the Texas incident last March,
but the attackers didn't do so.
Now don't you think that's kind of strange?
Then there's this unofficial FBI report.
Last December the U.S. Department of Defense held
a competition for the purpose of introducing new weapons.
Six companies, including Genom
and Gulf and Bradley competed.
When it was over, the winner was a GD-42,
a combat robot build by Qusai Industries,
of which Chang is chairman.
Formed from a base of Asian American immigrants,
the Chang conglomerate has had a antagonistic relationship
with Gulf and Bradley for over a decade.
- Well, why is that?
- Chang's son and daughter-in-law died 15 years ago.
- It seems to have been a murder
made to look like a traffic accident.
Gulf and Bradley were thought to have been behind it,
but they were not found guilty due to lack of evidence.
According to reports, Genom and Gulf and Bradley,
entered into their partnership this past January.
- So the Chang group is responsible?
- Maybe, but if so why did they wait 15 years for revenge?
(door thuds)
- [McLaren] What's your name?
- My name is Irene.
- That's a nice name.
(McLaren chuckles)
- Pretty good for a man his age.
This is the fourth night in a row.
- Tell me about it.
(McLaren moans)
(dramatic music)
- He suddenly clutched his chest moaning in pain.
- That's why he should've been more concerned about his age.
(dramatic music)
- They just left the room.
Looks like they're taking him to the hospital.
One of the bodyguards is still in the room
along with the call girl.
(dramatic music)
(police siren wailing)
- [Sylia] Be careful, Priss,
there's something funny about that ambulance.
- [Priss] Roger, Sylia.
- Hey, where are we?
Hey.
(body thuds)
(tires screeching)
(dramatic music)
- [Priss] Get out of the ambulance now!
You asshole!
Shit.
(Priss screams)
(machine whirring)
- I must have contracted Miss Reika's condition.
- [Paramedic] What do you mean the patient's gone?
Is this some kind of a joke?
- Why no, you see the ambulance already came.
- [Paramedic] What the hell does that make me?
- Hey, where we going?
- We're going back to the office?
- Then what?
- We open a kidnapping investigation.
(Priss breathing deeply)
- Sylia, I got whipped.
- Priss.
(gasping deeply)
- Why that's Irene's.
- Dr. McLaren is kidnapped.
Linna goes missing
and to top it off, Priss gets a broken arm.
Everything's going wrong.
- Whether Linna's transmission was cut off,
she was near Irene's grave,
and I have a feeling there's a connection.
Would you check the data on Irene?
- Mm-hmm, I hope Linna's not in danger.
(door thuds)
- I'm sorry we were so rough with you.
You were in Irene's letters, weren't you?
Were you a friend of hers?
- You're Reika, aren't you?
You're Irene's older sister.
Just what are you trying to do?
Tell me Vision.
(gasps deeply)
Irene told me her sister was a singer.
I didn't recognize you at first without your makeup.
But you're Vision there's no doubt about it.
- Mr. Kou, there's a phone call for you.
It's Mr. Chang.
- [Kou] It's been quite sometime Mr. Chang.
- How is it going, Kou.
- [Kou] We have McLaren,
and Miss Reika is still the same.
- Hmm?
Well, now how is Reika's fighting performance?
You must tell me the truth.
Speak frankly.
- Miss Reika is soft.
She can't bring herself to kill people.
Her hatred of Miss Irene's death
fuels her desire for revenge, but.
- It was my beloved granddaughter's wish.
Even I could not refuse her.
I didn't want to drag here into the shadow world, but.
- I understand how you feel, sir.
- Me, I am old, and you are the only one
upon whom I can rely now.
- We will protect Miss Reika
even if it costs us our lives.
- I am counting on you, Kou.
(dramatic music)
- [Reika] The Changs have led Hou Bang for generations.
- [Linna] Hou Bang?
- [Reika] A secret society, which was the basis
for my grandfather's success in the world.
After my father died,
there was a void in the Hou Bang successorship.
But I didn't particularly care
until she, Irene, was killed by Genom.
Then I was determined that I would have vengeance.
First on the chairman on Gulf and Bradley
for killing my parents and then--
- You think you're going to kill Quincy
with McLaren as your bait?
- [Reika] Yes, I'll kill him.
I'll teach him about the pain he has caused us.
- Look doing this for Irene's sake--
- Won't bring her back!
I know that.
I know it's pointless, but it hurts so much.
I can't let him get away with it.
- Reika, what will you do after you've killed Quincy?
You'll become the new head of Hou Bang.
What about your singing?
- I'll quit.
This tour was bogus from the beginning.
Strange, isn't it?
Time was I hated my own clan with a passion,
but now I think of it with great pride.
- [Scientist] Fluid temperature 23 degrees centigrade.
Ion concentration 75%.
Commencing armor plating.
(machine beeping)
- Mr. Quincy. - Yes.
The man who abducted McLaren.
- Is this Quincy?
- [Quincy] You people went to a lot of unnecessary trouble.
- Unnecessary?
- The boomer is finished, and McLaren is a closed subject.
You can boil him, roast him, do what you like with him.
- Are you sure? - Quite.
- No one knows the new type's weaknesses
and limitations better than McLaren.
Eastern Europe, the Middle East, Africa
lots of people will want McLaren.
Your new type will soon be unsalable.
No one will want a weapon
that's had all its secrets exposed.
- Then what are you demands?
- [Kou] I want to deal with you face-to-face.
I'll give you my demands at that time.
- You want to meet with me personally.
Will I be dealing with Mr. Chang?
- [Kou] That's right.
- Alright, suppose we meet at 1700 tomorrow
at artificial island D-35.
- Are you thinking of trying something underhanded.
- [Quincy] Is that an objection?
- No, tomorrow then.
- [Quincy] Prepare for testing.
Activate in two hours.
- [Scientists] Yes, sir.
- A public servant moonlighting.
Oh, I'd hate for anyone to find out, Nene.
(chuckling gently)
I want you to check the computer
for connections to this case.
Let me know as soon as you got anything.
(boat horn blowing)
- I understand you were a friend of Miss Irene.
I'm sorry about the cramped accommodations,
but I ask you to bear with them just a little longer.
That lock will automatically disengage in 24 hours.
Tomorrow night you will be free.
- Wait, are you gonna kill Quincy tomorrow?
Don't drag that girl into this.
Do you wanna make Reika, Vision a murderer?
Don't you realize she's just acting out of despair.
If you keep supporting her--
- What do you know?
You don't know how grief stricken Miss Reika was
when she lost Miss Irene!
To see Miss Reika smile again, I'd kill Quincy
even if he was a god.
- You're so wrong about this.
- Carl Baker's four o'clock piano concert
at the Yokohama Bayside Hall still has seats available.
Tickets for the (mumbles) combo go on sale
at the 20th of this month.
And, finally, the opening concert of Vision's tour
beginning tonight at the new Tokyo dome is sold out.
(copier whirring)
- [Sylia] Maybe I miss calculated.
- A chopper just left that lab.
Looks like it's heading for Genom tower.
(watch beeping)
- Linna?
Are you alright, Linna?
- [Linna] Priss.
- Hey, Nene, are you ready for tonight?
- What do you mean ready?
(gasping) The concert's tonight.
- You mean you forgot?
- [Nene And Naoko] Huh?
(gasping deeply)
(gentle music)
- Quincy's made his move.
Let's go. - I'll get the car, Leon.
- [Nene] Leon, I've got it.
- We'll talk in the car.
- [Priss] Come on, Linna.
(gentle music)
- So it's just you two after all.
Well, what are your demands?
- I demand your life.
(Quincy chuckling)
- [Quincy] For what reason?
- [Reika] Does the name Irene ring any bells?
- [Quincy] No.
- It's the name of my little sister who was killed
a year ago for the sake of your filthy rotten dreams.
- I know nothing about it.
I have far too many dreams, you see.
- Don't play innocent.
If you think I'm going to let you
get away with this, you're wrong.
- Well, then it just doesn't make any sense to me at all.
So a childlike you is going to take revenge.
(chucking sarcastically)
It's rather foolish of you to cause
such an uproar over just one little girl.
(gun firing)
- [Linna] You've got to stop this fighting now.
- [Reika] Linna!
- [Male] Shut up Genom agents.
- [Priss] A cold day in hell.
We're the-- - The Knight Sabers.
They and you are two of a kind.
Foolish rabble striking out at Genom.
- An android.
- Now that the components are assembled,
let's raise the curtain on the show.
(dramatic music)
- I'll shake it off.
- [Nene] This incident has its roots
in the murder of Irene Chang.
- [Leon] And the Texas incident?
- [Nene] It was for the killing of her parents.
- [Leon] And the culprit?
- It's Vision, I think.
Though I don't know if she's the principle one.
There are extenuating circumstances aren't there?
- Shit, this traffic we're not even moving.
(Priss yells)
- [Quincy] Let me give you some advice.
This town has a multitude of hidden surprises
and an inescapable surveillance network.
There is no place.
(Quincy laughing)
- [Priss] That sucker's mine.
(dramatic music)
- The monitor.
- [Priss] Can you see yet?
I'll be your eyes.
- [Linna] Reika, immobilize the thing.
- Linna, forget it.
Just get yourselves out of here.
- [Linna] It's too late.
(Kou grunts)
- [Linna] Disgusting.
- Kou, we'll blow it up with our self-destruct system.
- Did you copy that, Knight Saber?
- But what about you guys? - We've got an escape system.
Now get out of here.
- Arming self-destruct system.
- Reika!
- Reika! - Stay away.
- Get away there's no time.
- Let's get out of here.
(explosions echoing)
- [Linna] You better hurry or your concert's
going to start without you.
- It's okay, I'm not going to sing anymore.
Besides my revenge isn't finished yet.
Not until I kill Quincy.
- [Linna] How long are you gonna go on like that?
- But Irene won't rest in peace if I leave this undone.
What's this?
(gentle music)
- [Linna] Irene was a young girl in love.
She was so happy when she got this engagement ring.
It gave her hope.
Reika, I think there's another way besides revenge.
But only if you take Irene's hopes and see them through.
- Linna.
- A.D. Police.
- I'm glad you're here, officer.
Those are the people who kidnapped me.
- I'm the kidnapper.
She had nothing to do with it.
- Kou.
- Richard McLaren, you're under arrest.
On suspicion of violating the armaments construction laws.
- Wait a minute. - Not to mention
multiple counts of soliciting prostitution.
- [McLaren] Now come on.
- Miss Vision, we appreciate your help
in arresting this criminal.
Therefore, with your permission
we would very much like to escort you
to the concert grounds.
Would that be alright?
- Yes
(\"Never The End\")
♪ And on the forsaken streets
♪ In this weary town
♪ Refuge of the cold lonely hearts ♪
♪ Look up you'll see the sunrise flying all around ♪
♪ From within the walls of my broken heart ♪
♪ I heard the dawn whisper to me ♪
♪ If you search there's joy to be found ♪
♪ Just then I opened the door
♪ Wanting to feel life once more ♪
♪ My breath swept away by the glow ♪
♪ Of the ripe blue sky
♪ And now I don't miss a bright new day ♪
♪ A new light shows the way
♪ No longer lost because you've come down to shine ♪
♪ Through the shadows of lost dreams ♪
♪ My heart sings a sweet melody ♪
♪ All about you our souls meet
♪ And I understand that you've come across time ♪
♪ Just to show me that love never ends ♪
♪ No, never the end
♪ No, never