[SHADOW]
Majesty...
If I may say so,
you don't need to make
this trip yourself.
[MIRELIA]
The country's--
no, the entire world's
survival is at stake.
I will not sit here
and wait for news
when I still have the
strength within me to fight.
[SHADOW]
As you wish.
I apologize for this.
Not at all.
Your Majesty, we live for this.
[SOLDIERS gasping]
Today we go to war!
Pope Bisca T. Balmus
is a traitor.
It's time to put an end
to the Three Heroes Church
and its followers.
[SOLDIERS]
Right!
We leave immediately!
Cavalry, move out!
--[horses neigh]
--[SOLDIERS cheer]
Shield Hero, please
survive till I get there.
Our troops will be there soon.
Hang on, Melty.
And now for group defense
magic of the highest level:
Cathedral!
[bell tolls]
[REN]
Thunderbolt Slash!
Thunder Shot!
Filo! Raphtalia!
--Right!
--[FILO] 'Kay!
[FILO]
High Quick!
[RAPHTALIA yells]
[RAPHTALIA grunts]
[POPE groans]
[CLERGY praying]
[PRIEST 19A]
Heal my target!
Zweit Heal!
Filo!
One more time.
'Kay!
Grab him, too!
Huh? [screams]
Wait a sec!
Zweit Aqua Shell!
[MYNE gasps]
[ALL gasp]
Come on, Sister,
keep your focus!
[NAOFUMI] Okay, Motoyasu,
when we get close
I want you to attack me, got it?
Huh?! But why?!
[FILO grunts]
[MOTOYASU screams]
[NAOFUMI]
Now!
Fine, then! [grunts]
[yells]
He dispelled that
curse so easily.
[POPE]
All curses are meaningless
within the walls
of this Cathedral.
After all, we are standing
on hallowed ground
that has been blessed
by God himself.
[BOTH grunt]
[NAOFUMI groans]
[MOTOYASU groans]
[BOTH grunting]
Wow, he's so powerful!
Can you hear me
out there, Bishop?
I need the believers
to pray harder,
to show our enemy the
true might of God.
[PRIEST 19A]
But, sir, almost a third of them
have already given the last
of their mana to the cause.
If they don't stop now,
their lives may be in danger.
[POPE]
Is there a problem with that?
[PRIEST 19A gasps]
[POPE]
Don't forget,
this is a battle between
God and the Devil.
To perish here is
to become a martyr.
No disciple of the
Three Heroes Church
could hope for a higher honor.
[PRIEST 19A]
Yes, Your Excellency.
My brethren!
The Pope requires more prayers!
How can he causally throw away
the lives of his followers?
They all trusted in him!
Still do.
They'll follow that
order to the death.
[POPE]
Indeed.
We are one in body and soul.
With the help of their prayers
and the strongest attack this
sacred weapon can muster,
I shall grant you all
the purification
you so desperately deserve.
It is the greatest
mercy God could ever
bestow upon the likes of you.
Something about this
feels all wrong...
He's building up an
awful lot of mana.
If they keep praying,
that light will reach
the top of the Cathedral!
That's probably gonna be
when he launches
that huge attack.
Hey! How 'bout you
put that shield to use.
Can't it do something?
Huh?
[MOTOYASU] I mean, that thing
seems kinda overpowered.
Are you serious?
[ITSUKI]
He's right.
Compared to us,
you're way under-leveled,
but you're still
able to keep up.
Don't you think that's
because of your shield?
[NAOFUMI]
My weapon's not overpowered,
you just don't know
how to use yours!
Do you have any special
skills that might help?
If I did, don't you
think I'd be--
[NAOFUMI groans]
[NAOFUMI]
What's happening?
[NAOFUMI gasps]
[FITORIA]
Curse powers are impressive,
but the consequences are dire.
Please do not resort to
that power, Shield Hero.
Naofumi?
This might be a gamble,
but if we're lucky, it'll work.
That's what I like to hear.
Wait a minute. Are you
really gonna use it?
[NAOFUMI]
Mm.
It's worked out pretty
well in the past.
I'm sure I can handle
it this time.
'Kay. I will trust you.
I do, too.
[MELTY]
Mm.
[ZOMBIE DRAGON]
You made the right choice
to release me from my shackles.
[NAOFUMI gasps]
[NAOFUMI groaning]
[NAOFUMI yelling]
[ZOMBIE DRAGON]
Let the anger take control
and your suffering will end.
No, I...
I... won't!
[screams]
[NAOFUMI groans]
I won't let you...
You can't control me!
I'm not going to allow your
anger to overtake me this time!
[ZOMBIE DRAGON]
A dragon's fury is powerful,
but this is not my anger.
This rage wells up from
within your own heart.
[gasps] What?!
[gasps, groans]
[ZOMBIE DRAGON]
You're angry for being framed.
[NAOFUMI groans]
[ZOMBIE DRAGON]
You're angry for being hated
and publicly humiliated.
[NAOFUMI groans]
[ZOMBIE DRAGON]
You're angry for the persecution
you've had to face,
never having a chance
to defend yourself.
All that outrage is yours alone.
It's mine?
[ZOMBIE DRAGON]
Now release every last drop
of your pent up
resentment and scorn.
So much...
[ZOMBIE DRAGON]
Unleash the anger you have felt
against your enemies.
I can give you all
the power you need.
[NAOFUMI]
Power!
[gasps]
No, don't!
You can't let him
corrupt you like that!
Don't surrender to it...
[ZOMBIE DRAGON]
Did it not taste sweet?
[gasps]
[ZOMBIE DRAGON] Using the
power of the cursed flame,
how easily you could make
all your foes submit to you.
It felt good, did it not?
You felt fulfilled.
[NAOFUMI]
I...
[ZOMBIE DRAGON]
Let your rage show!
Seize that power!
Burn everything that
stands in your way!
[NAOFUMI]
Burn...
I'll burn it all!
[ZOMBIE DRAGON]
Good... Excellent, human!
Even my own rage is
nothing compared to this.
[ZOMBIE DRAGON chuckles, laughs]
Naofumi, you okay?
[MOTOYASU] Did he actually
become the Devil of the Shield?
Oh, no!
[NAOFUMI]
Burn everything...
[NAOFUMI] If I burn it all
down, this'll finally end.
[RAPHTALIA]
Master Naofumi!
My anger can take control,
and I can use it to
destroy everything.
[FILO]
Master!
[NAOFUMI]
I have the power to do that now.
I can do whatever I want.
[MELTY]
Naofumi!
[grunting]
You're so annoying!
Don't try to stop me!
[FILO]
You don't mean that, do you?
Do you really hate
everything, Master?
[NAOFUMI gasps]
That voice. Who are you?
[RAPHTALIA] We're your
friends, Master Naofumi.
Doesn't that mean
anything to you?
My friends?
[RAPHTALIA] In the beginning,
I was terrified.
I thought you were going
to treat me like an object
like everyone else always did.
But instead,
you were nice to me.
You cared for me.
You protected me.
Taught me right from wrong.
That's why I vowed to
always stand with you.
[FILO]
And as for me, you hatched me,
and you've been raising me since
the very first day of my life!
You gave me the wagon
I like to pull so much,
and my clothes,
and all sorts of fun stuff.
Pretty much everything
I love in this world,
I got from you!
[MELTY]
You were always stubborn,
never listening to me.
And you kept making fun of me.
Yet... you made good on your
promise to keep me safe.
Knowing that I was more
than just a princess,
you treated me like
a real person,
and became a true friend.
[NAOFUMI gasps]
[NAOFUMI]
That's right.
I've been on a journey...
...with friends!
People I care about,
that I swore to protect.
[MELTY]
You're not really the type
to wear your heart
on your sleeve,
so we never know exactly
what you're thinking.
[RAPHTALIA] But we do know that
you care about us, very much.
And we care about you.
Uh-huh! I love you
a whole bunch, Master.
And I'm gonna eat up
all your bad feelings
so you don't have to
feel them anymore!
I'll share your pain.
Whatever you need,
I'll be there.
I'll cut through your sorrow.
That's what I'm here for.
After all, I promised that
I'd always be your sword.
[NAOFUMI gasps]
[RAPHTALIA]
Master Naofumi!
[gasps]
My friends, thank you.
Thank goodness.
I'm so glad you came back to us.
Are you okay, Master?
That was too close!
We're all glad you're back!
I'm sorry...
I never meant to
hurt any of you.
[RAPHTALIA]
You did the right thing.
[NAOFUMI gasps]
You chose the path that
was meant for you.
We've traveled side by side.
We're in this together!
Raphtalia...
I'll keep on eating up
all your bad feelings.
Again and again,
until they all go away!
Filo...
[MELTY]
If you're feeling better,
could you hurry up
and figure out a plan?
We're kind of in the
middle of a battle here.
I'll get right on it, Melty.
[REN]
You all right?
Looks like something's different
about the berserk mode, huh?
Compared to the
last time we saw it?
[NAOFUMI]
I'm gonna need your help.
Are you serious?
[NAOFUMI]
Please.
[ITSUKI, MOTOYASU, REN gasp]
Now that's a word I
never expected to hear
coming out of you, Naofumi.
[REN]
Can we win?
I don't know,
but it's worth a shot.
[REN]
Mm.
I told you that we
were gonna have to
fight together in
order to defeat him.
Motoyasu?
I don't know...
[MOTOYASU]
All right, fine!
Whatever you need!
Let's prove the
bonds of friendship
are always strong
enough to prevail.
[ALL chuckle]
[ALL gasp]
[POPE]
I'm sorry to interrupt
whatever you're
in the middle of,
but my weapon is
ready to purify.
Now...
It's time to say goodbye,
Devil of the Shield!
[NAOFUMI grunting]
I can't believe you're
still standing.
Even a devil
shouldn't be able to
stop the full force
of the Cathedral.
[NAOFUMI] Great power
always comes at a price.
[NAOFUMI] For example,
this "divine" power of yours
has come at the cost
of your disciples.
And your life alone
won't ever be enough
to atone for that!
[POPE gasps]
[POPE]
Wait. That shield!
Now!
[BOTH]
Right!
[ALL]
Yeah!
[ITSUKI]
Thunder Shot!
I'm not finished yet!
Wind Arrow!
Zweit Aqua Shot!
[ADVENTURER 18A, 18B]
Zweit Air Shot!
Don't give him time to recover!
[FILO]
High Quick!
[grunts]
I won't fall for
that a second time!
We're just here to distract you!
[gasps]
Meteor Sword!
[POPE groans]
[NAOFUMI]
Ren, Raphtalia,
you two get in close
and set up a screen.
Then when he can't see...
[MYNE]
Zweit Power!
Can't believe I'm takin'
orders from Naofumi...
Damn it all!
If that's how it's gotta be,
I'll take it out on you!
Air Strike Javelin!
[groans]
[NAOFUMI]
"The bonds of friendship
will always prevail," huh?
Uh--
Shut up!
Get in there and finish him off!
May this sacred flame come forth
and cleanse everything
that it touches!
Phoenix Blade!
As source of thy power,
the Shield Hero
and I order thee!
Decipher the laws of creation,
consume the flame,
and give me power!
[BOTH]
Wrath Fire!
[screams]
Ha! He did it!
All right, let's finish this!
Yeah!
[POPE groans]
[NAOFUMI]
Hang on a sec!
Something's wrong.
[MOTOYASU]
Chaos Spear!
State of Emptiness.
No way!
[BOTH groan]
Motoyasu!
[REN yells]
[REN groans]
[MOTOYASU grunts] That's one of
my spear's most advanced skills
and he countered me
with my own ability.
[REN]
I don't believe it...
That weapon can imitate
anything we do with ours?
Your sins demand more.
You defy God!
Cleansing you won't be enough!
[ALL gasp]
[BOTH gasp]
[NAOFUMI]
Now what?
[NAOFUMI groans, growls]
--[POPE laughing]
--[FILO gasps, whines]
--Stay away from us!
--[POPE laughing]
[MOTOYASU yells]
[MYNE shrieks]
[MELTY]
No... No, please!
Stop it!
Damn! What the hell is this?
I don't--
[RAPHTALIA]
It's an illusion!
Some kind of skill.
That's got to be
how he's doing this!
[POPE] It's too late
to receive God's mercy.
Despair is all that's left!
You'll be crushed under the
weight of your own minds!
[NAOFUMI]
Everyone, watch ou--
[NAOFUMI groans]
Oh, no! [gasps]
[NAOFUMI]
Raphtalia!
[NAOFUMI growls]
You will be annihilated.
Not a speck of ash will remain.
There will be no evidence
of your existence
when this is over.
As source of thy power,
the queen orders thee.
Decipher the laws of creation,
surround my target in a cage
of ice, and hold him there.
All Dritte Fall: Icicle Prison!
[POPE gasps]
[gasps]
[POPE]
Impossible!
[FILO, MELTY gasp]
How can her magic reach me here?
The Cathedral should protect me!
[MIRELIA]
Hurry! Now's your chance!
[growls]
[NAOFUMI, ZOMBIE DRAGON]
Foolish sinner, I sentence you
to cast your screams unto
the heavens you worship!
The jaws of the dragon born from
my flesh shall swallow you,
and you'll become an offering to
the gods as you howl in pain!
Legendary Shield Skill:
Blood Sacrifice!
[ALL gasp]
[NAOFUMI groans]
[NAOFUMI]
Why...?
Fitting end for a devil.
His death came because he was
consumed by his own power.
[POPE]
Filthy monster.
After all you've done,
you should be grateful that God
still sees fit to purify you.
[gasps]
[POPE screams]
[POPE]
Why?
How can this be
happening to me?
I am an apostle of God himself!
I am the Pope!
This can't be!
[gasps]
[POPE screams]
So... I take it we won?
[ALL gasp]
It can't be...
The Cathedral is gone.
Which means that the Pope...
[horse neighs]
This battle is finally over.
Accept your defeat
and surrender.
Looks like the queen and
her military made it here.
Yeah.
[RAPHTALIA]
Master Naofumi!
[ALL gasp]
You'll be okay, just hang on!
[FILO]
Master, please, get up!
[MELTY]
He's lost a lot of blood...
What was that skill?
Could it be that Naofumi...
gave up his life for us...?
No, please... Master Naofumi!
Master Naofumi!
[FILO]
Master, can you hear me?
Answer me!
[MELTY]
Stay with us, Naofumi!
[MIRELIA] The Shield Hero will
not die today, I assure you.
[gasps]
[ITSUKI, MOTOYASU, REN gasp]
It's Mother!
[MIRELIA] I'm terribly sorry I
couldn't arrive sooner to help,
Sir Shield Hero
Naofumi Iwatani.
[NAOFUMI groans]
Aren't you...
I am the soverign ruler
of Melromarc, Sir Shield Hero.
Queen Mirelia Q. Melromarc.