[GLASS]
Oh, pardon me.
Whatever happened to my manners?
I am called Glass and that's
all you need to know for now.
Feel free to consider
me your enemy.
How'd she--
She took out that
Soul Eater in one hit!
If ya ask me,
she's just showing off.
I'm shaking. I can't stop.
I'm Naofumi.
[GLASS]
Naofumi? Well, well...
[GLASS] Then may I
suggest that we begin...
...the only battle of this
Wave worthy of the name?
In this empty void I
found the way to the light
Can't find my way
in this lingering world
Searching for the answer
the one that I can trust in
I'm just wandering around
Yeah, still stuck
in the shadow, ay
But I never follow that
This pain at last
Soon will pass
Turn into my own
unbeatable strength
This guy or that guy
dead or alive
by hiding alone we can't survive
I don't want to lie to myself
Keep on the fight, get right
I'll never lose and cry
Keep run up day and night
Time to rewrite
No matter what anyone say
I find my way, yeah
Never go away
Now, Nobody can stop me no way
I will make sure not to
forget those precious things
Yeah I'll take a stand
get back all that I've lost
Rise suddenly in this world
(I don't look back yeah)
This repetition will
repeat till the end
And the regrets are
still lingering in my head
Time to get it all back
now turn over
Rise suddenly in this world
(I don't look back yeah)
[GLASS] Why are you waiting
to attack, Hero Naofumi?
Why not try sending those
servants of yours at me first?
Servants?! What the hell--?!
You just called us...
...Naofumi's servants?!
[ALL]
Screw you!
Meteor Slash!
Meteor Thrust!
Meteor Shot!
[REN grunts]
[MOTOYASU yells]
[ITSUKI grunts]
[gasps]
[GLASS]
Is that all you've got?
Zero-Stance Rondo
Reverse Four Seasons.
[ALL scream]
[ALL groan]
As I was saying
before--mere servants.
[REN growls]
How did she do that?!
[MOTOYASU groans]
[GLASS] I hope you'll at least
entertain me a little.
Sorry, lady, but I never was
never much into entertaining.
That said, Shield Prison!
Raphtalia!
[RAPHTALIA grunts, gasps]
[FILO yells, gasps]
[NAOFUMI grunting]
You didn't really think
that would work, did you?
[NAOFUMI grunts]
Filo!
[FILO]
High Quick!
[FILO yelps]
Eight kicks in a second?
How very admirable.
But I'm afraid it's not enough.
[yells]
[gasps]
Not even worthy of mention.
[RAPHTALIA gasps]
Both of you,
get behind me--hurry!
Shield Prison!
Reverse Four Seasons.
[ALL grunting]
[NAOFUMI growls]
[GLASS]
I must say, I'm impressed
you're still standing
after all that.
Now then, when exactly
do you intend
to use that flaming shield
you've been wielding?
Master Naofumi...
Come forth, Rage Shield, now!
[NAOFUMI grunts]
[NAOFUMI yells]
[FILO yells]
I thought I was clear.
You can't touch me.
[FILO yells]
[RAPHTALIA]
Filo!
Raphtalia, take care of Filo!
[RAPHTALIA]
Huh?
[NAOFUMI pants]
[NAOFUMI grunting]
[gasps]
You can do better than that.
Your flame's too cold.
[RAPHTALIA gasps]
[GLASS]
Rupture-Stance Rondo!
Tortoise Shell Cracker.
[NAOFUMI grunts, groans]
Master Naofumi!
Interesting. Even that isn't
enough to bring you down.
If nothing else, your defense
lives up to your title of hero.
[NAOFUMI]
Flattery'll get you nowhere.
It seems, however,
your dark flame
only activates in
close-quarter attacks.
But the story is very different
when it comes to range attacks.
You have an ace up your sleeve.
Stop holding out on me.
Show me what you can do.
All right then, if you insist,
but don't say I didn't warn ya!
Shield Prison!
[NAOFUMI]
Change Shield!
Change to Iron Maiden!
[GLASS] Pity. It's even less
potent than I imagined it to be.
[NAOFUMI, RAPHTALIA gasp]
[GLASS]
How disappointing.
[NAOFUMI] Is there...
Is there nothing we can do?
[NAOFUMI gasps]
The time limit?
I didn't expect it
to hit this quickly.
[NAOFUMI gasps]
When I give you the sign,
use your light magic
to blind her.
[RAPHTALIA]
Mm.
The battle of the Wave
will end in our victory.
There can be no other outcome.
I have nothing against you,
but it is what it is.
Okay, now!
All right! Fast Light!
[GLASS grunts]
Fast Heal!
[NAOFUMI]
Let's go!
Of all the futile, useless...
She's attacking, Master Naofumi!
Air Strike Shield!
[NAOFUMI grunting]
So I can't defeat
him at this distance.
I shall leave this time,
but you won't survive
our next encounter
unless you get stronger.
Remember that
we shall be the ones
to emerge triumphant
from the Waves.
[RAPHTALIA gasps]
Is it all over?
[crash]
[ALL groan]
What happened?
Why did she allow
us to get away?
[VILLAGERS chattering]
[CHILDREN laughing]
[NAOFUMI] That countdown
showed up out of nowhere.
It must've been signaling
the end of the Wave.
[NAOFUMI]
But what are the Waves, anyway?
Weren't they supposed to be
world-ending calamities?
Why was that Glass woman so
fixated on defeating me, a hero?
...the only battle of this
Wave worthy of the name?
[NAOFUMI]
All questions and no answers.
But one thing's for sure:
we have to get much stronger
before the next Wave.
If we don't,
we'll be dead for sure.
Feeding my shield
monster fragments
will let me obtain new skills,
but any serious improvement
means Raphtalia and Filo
have to get class
upgrades, and soon.
Excuse me, uh, Sir Hero?
[NAOFUMI]
Yeah?
You are to report to
the royal castle at once.
Huh?
[NAOFUMI]
Shield Prison!
Time for... Change Shield!
[NAOFUMI, DRAGON ZOMBIE]
I cast the Iron Maiden!
[clears throat]
I saw what happened
through the crystal ball.
You did well to quell the Wave,
as much as I hate to admit it.
[NAOFUMI] Wow, don't be
grateful or anything.
Please, Sir Hero! I beg you!
I know how you feel.
Believe me, I understand!
But please go with the captain!
[sighs]
I have a question for you, Hero.
I want to know exactly
how you obtained
such incredible strength.
Huh?
[AULTCRAY] You possess powers
unbecoming of the Shield Hero.
It is your duty to reveal
the secret behind it.
It's time to spit it out.
And don't you even
think about lying to me.
[AULTCRAY]
Hm?
If you wanna know
so badly, come kneel.
[KNIGHTS gasp]
Y'see, where I come from,
when someone asks for something,
they usually grovel before the
one who has what they need.
[growls]
[NAOFUMI]
Oh, yeah, and they usually say,
"I beg you. Please deign to
enlighten my ignorant self."
Insolent cur!
As things stand now,
if I wanted,
I could kill you right here
and walk straight out the door.
You're bluffing and you know it!
[KNIGHTS gasp]
If any of you want to
fight me, go right ahead.
But I killed the Wave's
number one monster.
[KNIGHTS gasp]
[growls]
I'm willing to
cooperate with you
only until the Waves die down,
and then I'm going back home.
And don't even think
of calling me again.
I-I'm the king!
I forbid you to disrespect
me this way, Shield!
[gasps]
I know what to do.
Those slaves of yours
will pay for your crimes.
Don't think you can get
out of this that easily!
[NAOFUMI]
Huh?
[AULTCRAY gasps]
You can use all the dirty,
underhanded tricks
you can think of.
I'll protect my team
no matter what you do.
You'll never take
anything from me again.
I dare you to lay
a finger on them.
I'll chase you to
the ends of the earth
and make you regret
ever being born!
[AULTCRAY growls]
Accursed Shield!
You did well this time,
I daresay, Shield Hero.
I daresay.
Huh?
Your efforts have
become, shall we say,
somewhat impossible for anyone
to reasonably
ignore any longer.
Including certain powers who,
to put it mildly,
aren't taking too kindly
to your interference, Sir Hero.
Virtuous on the surface,
conniving and conspiring
behind the scenes...
You should exercise
the utmost caution
going forward,
I daresay. Understood?
"Daresay"?
[AULTCRAY] Aha, Melty!
What can I do for you?
I was told that you
and the Shield Hero
had a conversation just now.
Is that right, Father?
Huh? Uh?
And I was also told that
the conversation ended
in a very hostile manner.
[AULTCRAY groans]
[MELTY] Father, if you remain
at odds with the Shield Hero,
we may lose our only means
of fighting the Waves,
which could threaten the safety
of our entire country!
Please try to
reconcile with him!
Reconcile with that swine?!
[gasps]
O-Oh, don't worry, my dear,
I'm not angry at you.
I just don't understand, Father.
Why do you hate the
Shield Hero so much?
It's just that...
If he and his demi-humans
do as they please,
I'll lose my family again.
Father, I, uh--
[door opens]
[MYNE]
Your defiance is an affront.
[MELTY]
Hm?
[MYNE] With the queen away,
the king's word is final.
And not even we princesses
can go against it.
Sister, I...
[MYNE]
Our father is the king.
Whether you understand
his decisions or not,
they all have the betterment
of our country at heart.
I realize that you're
still at an age
where you want him to
baby you, of course.
I was once small
like you, too.
But you really should learn
to hold back a little,
dear Melty.
Just a word of advice
from your big sis.
I appreciate your concern
and I'm grateful,
but you see, Big Sister,
this is really none
of your business.
[MYNE grunts]
Just like our mother and father,
I only want what's best for
our subjects and our country.
You understand.
So, you see, it is
my job as crown princess
to see that everything
is put right.
Oh, Melty, you little...
[AULTCRAY sputtering]
[MELTY]
I'll take my leave now, Father.
[AULTCRAY gasps]
Melty, please, I--
[MYNE]
Papa.
[sighs]
[MYNE growling]
[ERHARDT] I can't believe
you actually went spoiling
for a fight with the king!
Well, better get
your facts straight.
He picked the fight.
Whatever. You can do
all your shopping here
since I've got everything.
But wait a sec. What about
the class upgrades?
Based on everything you've said,
it's unlikely they'll let you
use the dragon hourglass here.
[NAOFUMI] I was thinking
of going to either
Siltvelt or Shieldfreeden.
[ERHARDT] I always figured you'd
go to those places someday.
[ERHARDT]
I recommend Shieldfreeden.
Interesting,
that's the same place
the slave merchant
told me to go to.
He said for a
country of demi-humans,
it's quite welcoming to humans.
[ERHARDT]
Yeah.
Over in Siltvelt, they
can get pretty extreme
about demi-human supremacy.
But, as the Shield Hero--
Master, are we--
Are we really going
on another trip?
[NAOFUMI]
Mm-hm.
We're going on a trip!
Normally, it takes
about four weeks,
but I'm pretty sure she'll
get you there in less time.
I'll get everything ya need
loaded up on your wagon.
You're gonna have to
get goin' pretty quick.
Oh, and, um, I'd like a
new sword for Raphtalia--
Master Naofumi,
I already have a spare.
Wait a sec.
This is going to be
a long journey.
We should try to save money.
--[NAOFUMI sighs]
--[FILO giggles]
[RAPHTALIA] Erhardt is always so
fast and organized, isn't he?
We wouldn't have been able to
leave so quickly otherwise.
Yep.
Huh?
[ERHARDT] Just thought
I'd put in some gifts
for the road, kid.
Use 'em if ya like.
They may prove useful
on your journey.
[ERHARDT]
For you, a shield accessory.
It can analyze any shield,
besides doing tons
of other useful stuff.
[ERHARDT] For the little
missy, a brand new sword.
It's the same make
as the one she broke.
Nothing beats a trusty
old friend, right?
I put in another
one for her, too.
A mana sword.
[ERHARDT] For enemies
with no physical body.
[BOTH]
Hm?
[ERHARDT] If, God forbid,
your feathered lassie
can't draw the wagon anymore,
this little item
will come in handy.
She puts this on,
she'll gain the strength
of a hundred men!
Even you could
draw the wagon, kid!
[NAOFUMI]
Hmm.
Ooh. [giggles]
[groans]
[NAOFUMI chuckles]
[FILO whines]
[NAOFUMI exhales]
[NAOFUMI]
I love traveling.
It makes me feel free,
shackled by no one.
No royalty to deal with,
not even the other heroes.
[MELTY]
Found you!
[groans, sighs]
Huh? It's Mel!
Hey, we're over here, Mel!
--[NAOFUMI] Filo...
--It's so good to see you!
Master Naofumi, I know
it wasn't very long,
but we did travel
together as a team.
Mel's a good person, you know?
She really is!
Sir Shield Hero,
I have a request.
Please return to the capital
and speak with
King Aultcray again.
Not a chance.
[MELTY gasps]
I want you to apologize for
your conduct and reconcile.
Forget it!
[groans]
We need your help, Sir Hero.
We just can't stop
the Waves without you.
Besides, you'd be nowhere
without the king's
financial help.
Don't you understand?
What financial help?
I'm the one who's graciously
working with you guys--
only until all the Waves
are gone, that is.
Master Naofumi...
She's royalty, too.
[RAPHTALIA groans]
[MELTY]
Why...?
[BOTH]
Huh?
Why do both you and my father
have to act this way?
It's ridiculous!
[ALL gasp]
A hero and the king can't be
fighting among themselves!
Absolutely not!
[FILO]
Mel?
Don't you agree with me,
Filo? Isn't this silly?!
[FILO]
Uh...
You agree, don't you,
Raphtalia?!
Well, um, actually,
I am Master Naofumi's
sword, you know.
You see? They agree
with me--both of them!
Actually, they don't.
Look, just apologize to
Father, just this once!
Otherwise, Mother's
going to yell at him
when she comes back!
[NAOFUMI] She throws a
tantrum just like her dad.
Huh? Wait, what?
Her mother will yell at him?
You listen to me when
I'm talking to you!
[sighs]
[NAOFUMI]
Huh?
[gasps]
[NAOFUMI]
This feeling...
It's the same as
that other time.
[NAOFUMI]
This whole thing--
it reeks of a setup.
[NAOFUMI gasps]
So return to--
--[NAOFUMI grunts]
--[MELTY yelps]
[MELTY gasps]