[NAOFUMI] Off the coast of Cal
Mira in an underwater temple,
we found another
dragon hourglass,
alerting us to prepare
for the incoming Wave.
[NAOFUMI]
'Kay, Raphtalia?
[RAPHTALIA]
Sure.
Give me First Light.
[NAOFUMI gasps]
[NAOFUMI] No way!
That's a dragon hourglass!
If a Wave attacks this place,
the islanders will all die!
This says the next
Wave is coming...
...in just two days!
[NAOFUMI]
I used my teleport skill
and returned to the capital.
I explained things to the queen
and she immediately gathered her
army to prepare for the battle.
[NAOFUMI]
It was clear that this Wave
would most likely occur at sea.
So now we've boarded our ships
and we're just waiting to
be teleported to the Wave.
Actually, the queen was the one
who arranged for these ships.
And unlike that trash king,
she's a shrewd and
effective leader.
I don't know how,
but we made it.
Honestly I'm impressed
you managed to
put together an army
on such short notice.
Oh, it really wasn't a big deal.
Preparing for the Waves
is the royal family's
responsibility.
[NAOFUMI]
What are you doing here?
What's that supposed to mean?!
Uh--
[MELTY]
I'm here because...
...I'm part of your party.
I'm happy you're here.
I'm always happy when
I get to see you.
Aw, thanks, Filo.
I feel the same.
Do you think that the
people of Cal Mira
will be able to get off
the island in time?
[MIRELIA] The Earl of
Habenburg acted quickly.
He's already finished evacuating
all of the islanders.
Besides, we have
every reason to believe
this Wave will be
happening out at sea.
Right now, all you need to
worry about is the battle.
You got a point, but we sure
don't wanna get complacent.
And, no matter what,
the other heroes still don't
seem to wanna work together.
[MIRELIA]
They seem to think
leveling up at Cal
Mira was enough.
Yeah, and now it
looks like things are
about to get ugly again. [sighs]
[RAPHTALIA]
Master Naofumi.
[NAOFUMI]
Hm?
[RAPHTALIA]
It's L'Arc and Therese!
[NAOFUMI]
They're fighting the Wave, too?
You know them?
Yeah. They helped
us in Cal Mira.
I'm glad they're on our side.
They're more reliable
than the other heroes.
Wow.
It's not often you put so
much trust in other people.
[gasps]
It will begin when we teleport.
Everyone, prepare for battle!
Great. Here we go!
What are those?
Those are cask bombs.
They're made out of cohol fruit.
[NAOFUMI]
Hm?
Cohol fruit?
I get it.
Concentrated alcohol affects
monsters as much as people.
[SOLDIERS yell]
Do not let up.
Keep on firing at them!
Sir Itsuki!
[growls]
Meteor Shot!
[gasps]
[SAILORS yell]
We can't hit it unless we
get it out of the water!
[NAOFUMI]
Filo! Let's go!
[FILO]
You got it!
[NAOFUMI]
Lucky me.
[MIRELIA] Shield Hero,
we're going to need you
to keep the biggest
monster in check.
You make it sound so easy,
but don't forget,
that thing's underwater.
That's why it has to be you.
[FILO]
Huh?
[NAOFUMI]
Hate Reaction!
It took the bait!
[ALL gasp]
This is it! Time to attack!
Meteor Shot!
Meteor Thrust!
Meteor Slash!
[ALL]
All right!
[SAILORS screaming]
[MIRELIA gasps]
Well that's not good.
It doesn't even look like they
made a dent in that thing.
[RAPHTALIA grunts]
[growls]
Now that she's
leveled up a little,
Raphtalia's dealing a
hell of a lot more damage
than those three are.
But still, she can't
finish that thing.
Don't worry about the big one,
the heroes will have
to take care of that!
Focus on the little guys!
[CREW screams]
[SAILORS grunt]
[SAILOR 24B screams]
[roars]
[SOLDIER 24A]
Hurry up and kill these things!
No way! There's
too many of them!
As source of thy power,
I order thee.
Decipher the laws of nature
and thrash my targets
with a flood of water.
Zweit Aqua Shot!
You're okay, right?!
[SAILOR 24B]
Yeah. We're fine...
[MELTY gasps]
[MELTY screams]
[BOTH gasp]
[MIRELIA gasps]
No... Melty!
Melty!
[NAOFUMI grunts]
[MELTY whimpering]
[SAILOR 24B]
I've got you!
[SAILOR 24B grunting]
Melty!
[MELTY screams]
[L'ARC grunts]
You saved me...
Just sit tight for me, will ya?
Skybound Wheel Swing!
--Amazing...
--Uh-huh...
All right, now's our chance!
[SOLDIERS yell]
I can't believe how
powerful you are.
Naofumi was right about you.
Huh?
[NAOFUMI]
L'Arc!
It's time to get in there and
attack the big fella, 'kay?
Even if you fall into the water,
Filo and I will be
there to bail you out!
[L'ARC] Well, I guess it
does need to go down first.
All right, but get its big
ass out where I can hit it!
Go, Filo!
Yeah!
[L'ARC]
Skybound Wheel Swing!
You can't show me up!
[NAOFUMI]
Go for it, Filo!
[FILO yells]
[NAOFUMI]
Time to finish it!
[FILO]
Right!
Spiral Strike!
Bejeweled Thunderstorm!
Combo Skill:
Thunderbolt Wheel Swing!
I've never seen such a
remarkable display of strength!
[NAOFUMI] Nicely done.
Thanks for the assist.
Well, you weren't
gonna beat it alone
with that defense-
focused shield.
Thanks anyway.
[MOTOYASU]
Hey!
[gasps]
[MOTOYASU]
Naofumi!
You and your friend here
did a really good job.
What are you guys doing here?
We came for the
drops, obviously.
The items that the Wave
monsters drop after the battle
belong to all the heroes.
That might make sense
if you three did anything.
Look, guys, the one who
killed this thing was--
"Heroes"?
That your idea of a joke?
Because no one's laughing.
You weaklings can't
protect a thing.
Huh?
[ITSUKI gasps]
[RAPHTALIA]
The queen wants you to hurry up
and get rid of the
remaining monsters.
[MOTOYASU, ITSUKI, REN gasp]
[ITSUKI]
Ow... What the...?
Master Naofumi!
What do you think you're doing?
[L'ARC] I guess you really
are the Shield Hero, huh?
Hmph. All right then.
I guess it's come down to this.
What the hell are you
talking about, L'Arc?
[L'ARC]
It's simple really.
For the sake of our world,
you gotta die.
[L'ARC] For what it's worth,
we've got nothing against you.
[THERESE]
It's true. Please believe us.
This is unfortunate,
especially after you
were so kind to us.
But we really do
not have a choice.
Without us,
this world will be completely
powerless against the Waves!
We know. That's what
we're going for.
[NAOFUMI]
What?
[THERESE]
L'Arc, he'll understand
if you give him a
proper explanation.
[groans] This is such a pain!
Long story short,
the two of us are heroes,
just like you are.
From another world. Y'got it?
Another world?
[THERESE]
And just like your world,
ours is also teetering on
the brink of destruction.
There's only one way to stop it.
Do you mean...
[L'ARC] Basically, we've also
got something to fight for.
That's why we can't
afford to lose.
You understand, right?
But if we're gonna fight,
let's keep it fair and square!
So get ready, Shield Hero!
This whole time he's
only been after Naofumi?
I'm afraid we have no choice
but to mark them as
enemies of the heroes.
Listen up, those
adventurers are hostiles.
We will defend the heroes
and bring those two down!
[SOLDIERS]
Ma'am!
Okay, this isn't funny...
[REN groans]
You guys should've
just stayed down.
[MOTOYASU yells]
[L'ARC grunts]
Attack!
[L'ARC]
Therese!
Of course.
Power of jewels far and wide,
I beseech thee, heed my call.
Come to me!
[ALL grunting]
[THERESE]
My name is Therese Alexanderite.
My friends, be the force that
destroys my targets for me!
I cast Bejeweled Meteor Shower!
[NAOFUMI]
Raphtalia!
[RAPHTALIA grunts]
I'm fine!
Therese!
[THERESE]
I know. I'm only making sure
we aren't interrupted.
Now, my friends,
protect my targets from
the destruction around them!
Bejeweled Silver Lining!
[NAOFUMI]
First she attacks them,
and now she's helping them?
What are they thinking?
[L'ARC]
We're only here for Naofumi.
This isn't about you so
ya better just stay out of it.
That's right. We just
have one target.
[NAOFUMI]
You just want me?
So be it.
But Master Naofumi...
I understand.
If you're gonna be
mean to my Master,
I'm gonna kick
both of your butts!
[L'ARC grunts]
[NAOFUMI grunts]
[RAPHTALIA yells]
[FILO yells]
Air Scythe Suite.
[BOTH gasp]
[L'ARC]
First Stance: Wind Blowout!
[RAPHTALIA groans]
[L'ARC groans]
Oh, no!
I'm okay, he didn't
hurt me at all.
It does feel a little
bit numb, though.
Oh, man.
You sure know how to
keep things interesting.
[CREW chattering]
[MIRELIA] Priority one
is rescuing our men.
Move them to the
remaining ships.
[SAILOR 24A]
What about the heroes?
They're in the water.
[MIRELIA]
Their party members have already
taken rowboats to help them.
They can handle it.
[pants, gasps]
Oh, my! Princess Melty! [gasps]
Take this boat over
to Naofumi, now!
[RISHIA] Huh? B-But we
just barely got back
from rescuing Sir Itsuki
from over there!
Just shut up and do it!
[RISHIA whining]
Is that the same move?!
[groans]
Oh, no!
[BOTH grunting]
[NAOFUMI]
How'd that happen?
I blocked his attack,
but I still got hurt.
--[gasps]
--[THERESE] Bejeweled...
...Sin Flame!
[JEWEL]
I'm sorry.
What was that?
[THERESE]
Of course.
You don't want to
fight him, do you?
[NAOFUMI] Is it because I
made that bracelet for her?
Therese!
[THERESE] It's fine.
I'll use a different one.
[NAOFUMI]
Drink up, you two.
--Okay!
--'Kay!
[NAOFUMI]
What is it with L'Arc's attack?
Does it ignore defense?
[NAOFUMI] No. I wouldn't
have taken that much damage
from just the tip of his weapon.
[NAOFUMI]
I've got a hunch.
I gotta say,
I wasn't expecting a
defense-reversing attack.
[L'ARC]
You got it.
The higher that my
target's defense is,
the more damage that attack
is gonna deal to them.
In other words,
it's the perfect counter
against the Shield Hero.
[gasps]
[L'ARC]
You were just guessing, huh?
Luckily for you,
my policy is to fight fair.
I have no secrets.
[NAOFUMI]
He wants to "fight fair"?
But we're trying to
kill each other!
[NAOFUMI]
He's done this before.
Trying to throw me off my game.
[MELTY]
Naofumi!
[FILO]
It's Mel!
[NAOFUMI]
How'd you get here?
I commandeered a ride.
[whines]
You haven't finished
this Wave yet.
So hurry up and beat
these guys already,
then finish the Wave
so we can go home!
[chuckles]
[MELTY]
Wh-What?
Nothin'.
L'Arc. You've got
a sound strategy.
Those defense-reversing attacks
will totally mess me up...
...unless I figure out
how to dodge all of 'em.
They'll be worthless
against my Air Strike Shield
and Second Shield.
[chuckles]
[NAOFUMI]
So I will use them if I have to.
Naofumi!
Why would you tell him how
you're going to defeat him?!
It's fair.
Looks like we've both got
our cards on the table.
In that case,
let's do it!
--[L'ARC grunts]
--Filo!
[L'ARC grunts]
[grunts] He's using venom?!
[THERESE]
L'Arc!
Zweit Aqua Shell!
[RAPHTALIA grunts]
An illusion?
[FILO yells]
Gotcha!
You fell for it!
[NAOFUMI]
Dog Bite!
[L'ARC grunts]
[BOTH] Create a storm
to blow them away!
Typhoon!
[yells]
I knew you'd do that.
[groans]
[RAPHTALIA grunts]
[yells]
[THERESE]
Protect him!
[L'ARC pants]
[NAOFUMI] He's still standing
even after our best combo?
[L'ARC]
Honestly, that really hurt.
You know how to make
perfect use of that shield,
don't you, kiddo?
You are good!
When you told us you'd be using
Air Strike Shield for defense,
we never imagined
that you'd actually
use it as a trap against us.
And you're good at
mind games, too.
[NAOFUMI]
Therese can switch between
offense and defense at will.
She deliberately
used that AOE spell
to make us stop our
attacks against L'Arc.
They're not lying.
They really are heroes
from another world.
Their spirit.
Their strength.
Honestly, they're more heroic
than the "heroes" here.
Stop it!
[L'ARC]
I was bored out of my mind
fighting those
monsters on Cal Mira.
But there's nothing better
than a man-to-man battle
with real strategy involved.
[NAOFUMI] This isn't the time to
be admiring how worthy they are.
It's kill or be killed.
I know that, and yet...
[L'ARC]
Isn't this fun, Naofumi?
[gasps]
We've got plenty
left in the tank.
How about you?
[grunts]
[GLASS] Will you please
stop fooling around?
[gasps]
[CREW screaming]
It's Glass.
Well hello there, Glassy.
What are you doing here?
I got tired of waiting.
Who is that woman?
Just the sight of her
makes me shiver.
That's Glass.
She almost killed us
during the last Wave.
And now...
...it appears that
she's on their side.
So good to see
you again, Naofumi.
[NAOFUMI] I can't say
the feeling is mutual.
Well...
Zero-Stance Rondo:
Reverse Four Seasons.
Rupture-Stance Rondo:
Tortoise Shell Cracker.
[NAOFUMI grunts]
From the looks of his shield,
you haven't seen his best yet.
His best? What do you mean?
When he gets serious,
he brings out something that's
--far more ominous.
--Huh?!
You did that much damage to
L'Arc and blocked my attacks,
all without using
your trump card.
You have grown
stronger, Naofumi.
Jeez, are you tryin'
to flatter me now?
Don't get cocky.
You can see now that I must
do this with my own hands.