[CREW groaning]
[SOLDIER 25A] Your Majesty,
everyone's accounted for.
[MIRELIA] I am thankful
for all your hard work.
--[explosion]
--[BOTH gasp]
[MIRELIA] The Wave is
showing no signs of stopping.
Perhaps that means it
won't end until those
adventurers have
finally been defeated.
Either way, there's
nothing we can do.
We'll have to entrust our
victory to the Shield Hero.
[GLASS yells]
[NAOFUMI grunts]
[NAOFUMI]
She thinks the Wrath Shield's
my only defense against her.
[BOTH grunt]
Master Naofumi!
[GLASS gasps]
[NAOFUMI gasps]
The Soul Eater Shield did that?
[NAOFUMI]
It drains the enemy's SP...
But still, I've never seen
Glass hesitate like that.
[THERESE]
I pray, may your sacrifice
carve open a path to our future!
Bejeweled...
Meteor Shield!
[THERESE]
...Compressor Bomb!
What magic is this?
It looks like it's being
powered by her jewels. [gasps]
That's the attack that
beat the others last time!
Power of jewels far and wide.
Heed my call and
come here to me.
[NAOFUMI] Crap! They can
use combo skills, too?
[THERESE]
My friends,
summon a freezing storm
that destroys my targets!
Shield Prison!
Bejeweled Blizzard!
Combo-Stance:
Reverse Hail Seasons!
[NAOFUMI grunting]
[GLASS gasps]
[NAOFUMI panting]
Master Naofumi!
Hey, are you holding up okay?
Yeah. I'm just peachy.
We can't even beat you
with that combo skill?
You have gotten better.
Everything I thought
I knew about you
is completely useless now.
Guess it's a good
thing we leveled up
back on Cal Mira, huh?
Yeah!
[FILO giggles]
[NAOFUMI] But something's
still bugging me.
Glass's reaction to the Soul
Eater Shield wasn't normal.
I wonder...
All right, new plan.
It's clear to me now that I
need to fight Glass alone.
No way! Are you
out of your mind?
[NAOFUMI] You three can
handle L'Arc and Therese.
Please don't tell me
that you're going to...
[NAOFUMI] This way I won't
have to use that shield.
Sounds good to me.
If that's the case,
then you can sign me up.
Yeah! I'm on board, too!
Let's go!
[GLASS gasps]
You can't get away!
[RAPHTALIA]
The two of you are going to
have to deal with us now!
[chuckles] Sounds like fun.
[GLASS chuckles]
Ah, a one-on-one fight?
Well, that's exactly
what I was thinking.
Although...
You're letting them fight a duo
as strong as L'Arc and Therese?
You're placing an awful
lot of trust in your party.
L'Arc told me he's a hero,
it's just that he's fighting
on behalf of another world.
[GLASS gasps]
I take it you have
the same story, Glass?
That's correct.
I am also what the
people of my world
call a Vassal Wielder--
the Fan Hero.
[NAOFUMI]
"Vassal Wielder"?
En garde!
[THERESE] My friends,
bring forth a wall of fire
to stop my targets
in their tracks!
Bejeweled Flame Bulwark!
Zweit Aqua Slash!
[L'ARC grunts]
I don't think so!
Damn it.
--[yells]
--[L'ARC grunts]
Heh. You guys are good.
No wonder Naofumi trusts you.
Hope he's all right...
[NAOFUMI] She's quick,
but she doesn't have
the edge on me she used to.
I can take her.
[GLASS] Rupture-Stance Rondo:
Tortoise Shell Cracker!
[NAOFUMI]
Dog Bite!
[GLASS gasps]
[NAOFUMI] Change Shield!
Soul Eater Shield!
[GLASS screams]
[NAOFUMI]
My hunch was right!
[NAOFUMI] Glass is weakened
by the Soul Eater!
Glassy's in trouble!
Naofumi...
[NAOFUMI] All this shield does
to anyone else is drain SP.
But with you, it seems to
suck out your life force.
[gasps]
This fight's over.
The Wave will die down
if you retreat, won't it?
So how 'bout we both
just call it a day?
"Call it a day"?
Oh, no. This battle's
not over just yet.
Not until one of us is dead.
I will never surrender!
Hey!
[GLASS screams]
Stop it, now!
If you don't, you're
gonna kill yourself!
[GLASS]
As long as I still draw breath,
I will do everything in
my power to end your life.
For the sake of the world
I love, I have no choice!
[NAOFUMI gasps]
[GLASS] So the only way
you'll ever be able to
get rid of me is if you kill me!
Otherwise, this world will end!
That's ridiculous!
Master Naofumi...
[GLASS] You're just like me,
aren't you, Naofumi?
You want to protect
this world, right?
Then you should want me
dead right here and now!
I, uh...
[NAOFUMI]
Protect it? Is that what I want?
The world I was summoned
to against my will?
Where I've been
put through hell?
She wants to protect
her world so badly.
So why have I been
fighting the Waves?
[gasps]
[NAOFUMI]
What is this?
[GLASS]
They're all waiting for us.
[NAOFUMI gasps]
My people are fighting
against their own Wave,
awaiting our triumphant return.
[NAOFUMI]
Am I seeing her world?
[GLASS]
That's why I cannot lose!
[gasps]
That's how this ends.
It's do or die, Naofumi!
[NAOFUMI] Am I willing to
destroy all her hopes
just to protect this world?
[L'ARC]
Heads up, Glassy!
[NAOFUMI]
Soul soothing potion?
All it does for me is give me
access to a few more skills.
But for Glassy...
[NAOFUMI]
Crap!
[GLASS yells]
--[NAOFUMI grunts]
--[RAPHTALIA] Master Naofumi!
[NAOFUMI groans]
[NAOFUMI]
Raphtalia!
What do you think you're doing?!
You know what I'm doing here.
I'm Master Naofumi's sword!
[NAOFUMI gasps]
Never again.
I won't let it happen.
No one else will ever go
through what Rifana and I did!
Got that?
Raphtalia...
You see, we have our
own reasons not to lose!
No, you don't!
Air Strike Shield!
You okay?
[NAOFUMI grunts]
[NAOFUMI]
Dark Gas Burning!
[BOTH gasp]
Naofumi! Raphtalia!
Glassy! Get outta there! Now!
[MIRELIA gasps]
This isn't good.
I wish there was
something we could do
to help them win this fight.
[RISHIA]
Someone please help me!
[MIRELIA gasps]
[whines]
I've got it!
[NAOFUMI gasps]
Still not giving up?
[panting]
Wait a sec... [gasps]
Enough. Let's end this.
[L'ARC]
You can't! It's too risky!
[THERESE]
You've done enough, Glass!
Blank-Stance Rondo...
Don't do it, Master Naofumi!
Don't use that shield!
I'm really just
an outsider here.
As soon as I finish
fighting off the Waves,
I'm just gonna go
back to my own world.
[RAPHTALIA gasps]
[NAOFUMI]
But you three--
Raphtalia, Filo, Melty...
This world has you.
That's my reason
for using this shield.
And it's the only reason
I need to take Glass down!
Don't do this...
Now, sinner, I sentence you
to cast your screams
unto the heavens above!
No, wait... Stop it, please!
[NAOFUMI] The jaws of the
dragon born from my flesh
shall swallow you, and
you'll become an offering
to the gods as you howl in pain!
[RAPHTALIA]
No!
[NAOFUMI yells]
Blood Sacrif--
[MIRELIA]
Shield Hero!
[gasps]
As source of thy
power, I order thee.
Decipher the laws of nature
and unleash a gust of wind.
Fast Wind Blow!
[RISHIA]
Here! You can use these!
Perfect!
Meteor Shield!
[gasps]
Wait, what did you do that for?
What the hell is this?
Oh, no. C'mon!
[NAOFUMI] They were
filled with cohol berries.
[RAPHTALIA] Aren't those
what they use to make wine?
[NAOFUMI]
Yeah, but for some reason,
they don't seem to
have any effect on me.
So? Finished yet?
No way. I'll kill you.
[gasps]
[NAOFUMI]
L'Arc?
[RAPHTALIA]
Therese!
[L'ARC] This fight's
over. We're outta time.
[L'ARC] So congrats.
I guess you win this round.
[THERESE] But this won't be the
last time we meet in battle.
What do you two
think you're doing?
If we don't kill
Naofumi right now...
[L'ARC] Yell at us when you're
not about to throw up, huh?
See ya 'round, Naofumi.
Heh. Feels wrong
to call you that.
Think I'll stick with "kiddo."
L'Arc, wait...!
[MYNE]
Sir Motoyasu!
[MOTOYASU groans]
The Wave. Did we win?
Looks like it's over anyway.
Naofumi soloed it again?
No. Every one of us
played our part here.
We share this victory!
[CREW cheering]
[whines]
I hate wine. [hiccups]
[RAPHTALIA] Oh, Master
Naofumi! An accessory shop!
Let's take a look.
[NAOFUMI]
Once the Wave was over,
we decided that we
were done leveling up.
We were going to leave
Cal Mira's bonus field behind
and head back to Melromarc,
except...
[RAPHTALIA] See those dark
clouds out there on the horizon?
It won't be safe for us to
sail back through those.
You know an awful lot
about the sea, huh?
Wow! You keep catching so many!
I did grow up in
a fishing village.
Yeah. Almost forgot.
[NAOFUMI]
Because of the offshore storm,
we decided to extend our
holiday for a few more days.
And yet... I still
couldn't relax.
L'Arc and Glass said they were
heroes from another world...
...who were trying to
fight off their own Waves.
In order to defend their world,
they have to defeat heroes
from somewhere else.
In other words,
they have to defeat us.
[RAPHTALIA] So when we get
back... what are we going to do?
[NAOFUMI] Well, prepare for
the next Wave, of course.
[RAPHTALIA]
Right.
[NAOFUMI] But... if we have to
fight Glass's party again...
...will I be able to kill them?
I can't tell you how many
Waves will have passed
when it happens,
but a time is coming when
the world will demand
great sacrifices from all of us.
There will be a battle
in which the heroes
will have to choose what
they're fighting for.
[NAOFUMI] So we'll have to
choose which world to sacrifice?
Is that what you meant, Fitoria?
[RAPHTALIA] Master Naofumi?
Is something on your mind?
Well...
I was just thinking it
might be time to start
recruiting some new
additions to the party.
That's a good idea.
After all, Melty's busy
with her royal duties now.
Let's gather as many weapons
and party members as we can.
Who knows how strong Glass's
party will be next time.
Huh?
[NAOFUMI] If the Four
Cardinal Heroes end up dead,
you guys will be this
world's only hope.
Well, uh...
[FILO]
Master, come quick!
[RAPHTALIA]
Hm?
You wanted to drown?!
[RISHIA whines]
[FILO]
Yeah, but I saved her!
[NAOFUMI]
Wasn't she in Itsuki's party?
She told me her name was Rishia.
I guess the Bow Hero kicked
her out of his party.
She said she's lost
hope completely.
He kicked her out?
She was accused of
something she didn't do.
[gasps]
[RISHIA]
I-I swear, it wasn't me!
They said I broke one of Master
Itsuki's favorite accessories,
but I didn't do it!
That's awful.
But it gave them an
excuse to get rid of her.
[NAOFUMI]
If I had to guess,
I'd say the rest of his
party was embarrassed
by her stealing the
spotlight in the Wave.
Knowing Itsuki,
he just trusted their accusation
blindly and threw her out.
[RISHIA cries]
Master Itsuki doesn't want
anything to do with me!
I don't deserve to live!
[NAOFUMI]
Rishia, right?
C'mon. Are you really
gonna take this lying down?
Well, they're not wrong
about everything they said.
I really am weak and useless.
Don't you want to teach Itsuki
and the rest of his party
a lesson for what
they've done to you?
You helped me out
a lot during that Wave.
[RISHIA gasps]
[BOTH]
Mm-hmm!
[RISHIA] Really?
I helped the Shield Hero?
You did. You saved everyone.
And you have the courage
to grow so much stronger.
Do you believe that?
You really think
I'm brave and strong?
Yes. Why don't you
join our party?
I'd be happy to help
out however I can
until you're able to
clear your name.
[gasps]
[RAPHTALIA]
Let's get stronger together.
[FILO] And maybe I can
teach you how to swim.
[RISHIA sobs]
Thank you!
Thank you so much for
inviting me to join with you!
Now you're training someone
else's party member?
You've become a
big softie, Naofumi.
[NAOFUMI] If their parties
are as useless as they are,
it'll cause real
problems for everyone.
[stomach growls]
[FILO]
Hey, where's the food?
[NAOFUMI, RAPHTALIA laugh]
[NAOFUMI] Right.
How 'bout we eat something?
--[RAPHTALIA] Great!
--[FILO] Yeah!
[NAOFUMI] Before long,
the storm died down,
and we were on our
way back to Melromarc.
[MIRELIA]
Thank you again, Shield Hero.
Words cannot
express my gratitude
for everything you've done.
I couldn't have done any
of these things by myself,
without my friends.
And many thanks to
you, too, Your Majesty.
You're giving me
too much credit.
[NAOFUMI] I don't know if
we'll be so lucky next time.
The other heroes are
still completely useless.
[MIRELIA]
I couldn't agree more.
[NAOFUMI] Guess I need to
try and talk to them again.
[MIRELIA] Yes. And sooner
rather than later.
By the way, Shield Hero,
did you ever figure out
the reward you wanted?
[NAOFUMI]
Hm?
[MIRELIA] I still have to
find a way to repay you
for the part you played in
eliminating the pope, remember?
Oh, yeah...
[MIRELIA]
And now there's so much more
that you've done
here in Cal Mira.
If I don't do something soon,
I'll never be able to repay you.
[NAOFUMI] Hmm. Actually,
I might have an idea.
Of course. I should've guessed
you'd request something
selfless like that.
[ERHARDT]
Oh, welcome back, kid!
Hey, where'd you pick up
a cutie a like this?
Ugh, give it a rest.
I need you to put together
some equipment for all of us,
including her.
I'll buy whatever I can,
as thanks for last time.
Now that's what I like to hear!
You planning to stick
around for a while?
[NAOFUMI]
Nah, just a pit stop.
There's somewhere we need to be.
Oh, yeah, I almost forgot.
Where are we going?
What are you guys talking about?
[ERHARDT]
Oh! Uh, nowhere special...
Isn't that right, kid?
[NAOFUMI]
Right.
[RAPHTALIA] What's with
you two? C'mon, just tell me!
You know, you sure are
a lucky little lady.
Huh?
Come back if you need anything.
My door's always open!
[RAPHTALIA]
Master Naofumi?
Yeah?
Can't you at least
tell me something
about where we're going?
[NAOFUMI]
Oh, sorry, uh,
we're on our way to
claim the queen's reward.
The one you were talking
about on the boat?
[sighs] You will stay with us,
right, Master Naofumi?
Mm?
Is that salt I smell?
[NAOFUMI chuckles]
I should've known.
You noticed that, huh?
[RAPHTALIA]
Does that mean...
[NAOFUMI]
Yep. We're almost there.
[RAPHTALIA gasps]
[KEEL]
Mm? Hey, it's Raphtalia!
Hi there, Keel!
You look good.
I'm glad you recovered!
[VAN]
Recovered so well, in fact,
that Keel's working
harder than everyone else.
Oh, hey, Van,
what are you doing here?
I see. You still don't
know why you're here?
[RAPHTALIA]
What?
[MELTY] Yeah... Naofumi's
still a really big jerk.
[FILO gasps]
Hiya, Mel!
Master Naofumi, will you please
tell me what's going on?
[NAOFUMI] Mm... You'll
find out soon enough.
[RAPHTALIA, FILO gasp]
[MELTY] In the name of
Queen Mirelia Q Melromarc,
I, Second Princess
Melty Melromarc,
hereby bestow Seyaette's
Demi-Human Region
to the Shield Hero,
whose name is Naofumi Iwatani,
along with all governing rights.
What?
[NAOFUMI] Surprise.
That was the queen's reward.
I'm officially the
lord of this area.
Are you all being serious?
[NAOFUMI]
The way I see it,
we're gonna need some
kind of home base.
[MELTY] You could've
lived in the capital
if you wanted to, you know.
[NAOFUMI]
Yeah, but if I did that,
it'd only be a matter of time
before I'd run into
Trash or Bitch.
[MELTY sighs]
[FILO]
Can we go play, Mel?
[MELTY]
Mm!
Raphtalia, come with me.
I want to show you something.
[RAPHTALIA gasps]
[RAPHTALIA]
Boats?
[NAOFUMI]
Restarting the fishing business
will help as we rebuild.
And we do have our
own fishing expert.
Me?
What do you think about showing
some of these
newcomers the ropes?
[NAOFUMI]
This way.
Well, if it isn't
the Shield Hero!
[NAOFUMI]
Workin' hard, I see.
I'll train as many new recruits
as you can scrounge up
and bring to me.
I know and I'm counting on it.
I've already got a trainee
with a lot of potential.
[OLD WOMAN 06A laughs]
I can hardly wait!
[HERBALIST 01A]
Hey! I've stocked us up
with plenty of medicine.
[MAGIC SHOPKEEPER 05A]
If you need anything else,
just let us know!
So all of you moved to Seyaette?
As soon as they found out
that I was the new local lord,
they insisted on
coming to help out.
[RAPHTALIA gasps]
[NAOFUMI]
At this rate,
the rebuild will be
finished in no time.
Why here?
I chose this place
a long time ago.
Your village was once
destroyed by a Wave,
but now it'll be a symbol
of resistance against them.
Rishia won't be the
last person we recruit.
We'll train them all
here and build an army
bigger than the rest of
the heroes have combined.
That way, if something--
[gasps]
Raphtalia?
Master Naofumi, please, I can't!
It's too much!
It feels like... like you're
trying to prepare us
for when you're not going
to be around anymore!
It doesn't matter if
Glass, L'Arc, and Therese
show up again, we can beat them.
We can beat the
Waves! I know it!
You're not going to die, Master
Naofumi! I won't let you!
Raphtalia...
[RAPHTALIA]
But, that doesn't really matter.
Because once we
beat all the Waves,
you're just gonna go
back to your world,
and I'll never see you again.
I never want that day to come!
[NAOFUMI]
Yeah, well...
[RAPHTALIA]
Never! I won't accept it!
Just imagining a life without
you--it's absolutely unbearable!
Because I... I just
don't want you to go!
Please, Master Naofumi!
Please stay!
Even after the Waves are gone,
stay with us forever!
[NAOFUMI gasps]
[RAPHTALIA sobs]
This has been on your
mind for a while...
[NAOFUMI]
I'm so sorry.
[RAPHTALIA] Oh, no.
You don't have to apologize!
I'll be honest,
I wasn't sure before.
[NAOFUMI]
But... I am now.
That's why I came here.
[NAOFUMI]
We're gonna start over.
If we're fighting the Waves or
looking for new party members,
it all begins here.
When I met you, I found meaning
in having to fight the Waves.
Meeting Filo and Melty helped me
decide to fight for my friends.
And I've met so
many other people
that have made me want
to be the Shield Hero,
and protect this world.
It's going to be
our new beginning.
More importantly, our home.
Master Naofumi...
Raphtalia, you'll keep on
fighting as my sword, won't you?
Yes. Of course I will,
Master Naofumi!
[FILO]
Hey, that's no fair!
[BOTH gasp]
[FILO]
I want a hug! Master!
--[FILO giggles]
--[NAOFUMI gasps]
Come on! Get in on this, Mel.
[MELTY gasps]
No thanks, I-I'll pass!
[KEEL, HERBALIST 01A laugh]
[KEEL]
Ready?
Ta-dah!
[VILLAGERS cheering]
Are you watching, Rifana?
Can you see the flag flying
over our village again?
And it's such a
beautiful flag, too.
[gasps]
[RAPHTALIA]
Master Naofumi?
Yeah. Our story begins anew.
A fresh start for
the Shield Hero!
Looks like Naofumi's settled
down in his own domain.
Guess it's up to us to
travel around the world
and make it a better place.
[REN]
I'll be so much stronger.
Stronger than you could
ever hope to be, Naofumi!
I can't believe the queen
gave the Devil of the Shield
his own domain.
Isn't it outrageous,
Sir Motoyasu?
Nah, I don't think so.
In fact, we should
visit him some time.
I'd like to see Filo, anyway.
[MYNE gasps]
Hmph.
It might behoove you to
keep an open mind, I say.
"Behoove"?
Huh? Yeah, why'd I say that?
[AULTCRAY] I'm counting
on you two, you know.
--[MIRELIA clears throat]
--[CONSPIRATORS gasp]
[sighs]
[SLAVE TRADER laughs]
That Shield Hero
certainly knows how to make
bold decisions, doesn't he?
I suppose it'll be a while
before he comes to see me again.
Remember, dear, you'll
always be my golden goose.
I have faith that you'll become
a better patron over time
and bring me greater
profits than ever.
[SLAVE TRADER laughs]