[ERHARDT humming]
--[door opens]
--Huh?
Welcome.
Come on, don't come
here to show off
every time you get a new slave.
Guess again.
[ERHARDT]
Another young girl?
You really are a lolicon, huh?
[NAOFUMI]
Don't be ridiculous!
Master, couldn't I have
just a little snack?
Want a bite? Knock yourself out.
Thanks!
Filo, don't overdo it.
Hey, relax. It's fine, miss.
How big a bite could
she take, anyway?
Time to dig in!
[FILO]
That wasn't too bad actually.
In this empty void I
found the way to the light
Can't find my way
in this lingering world
Searching for the answer
the one that I can trust in
I'm just wandering around
Yeah, still stuck
in the shadow, ay
But I never follow that
This pain at last
Soon will pass
Turn into my own
unbeatable strength
This guy or that guy
dead or alive
by hiding alone we can't survive
I don't want to lie to myself
Keep on the fight, get right
I'll never lose and cry
Keep run up day and night
Time to rewrite
No matter what anyone say
I find my way, yeah
Never go away
Now, Nobody can stop me no way
I will make sure not to
forget those precious things
Yeah I'll take a stand
get back all that I've lost
Rise suddenly in this world
(I don't look back yeah)
This repetition will
repeat till the end
And the regrets are
still lingering in my head
Time to get it all back
now turn over
Rise suddenly in this world
(I don't look back yeah)
So what's the story here?
[RAPHTALIA]
According to the slave merchant,
filolials have a king or
queen leading each flock.
That's what he told us, anyway.
[ERHARDT]
I thought that was just a myth.
[RAPHTALIA] Those kings and
queens are highly skilled
at transforming, and they
blend into the flocks
by disguising themselves
as normal filolials.
[ERHARDT] And they can transform
themselves into humans, too?
That's nuts.
[NAOFUMI] What's more, it turns
out they need a special crest
to be tamed.
I hadn't budgeted for that.
[RAPHTALIA]
Things got crazy
while trying to
give her that crest.
Filo started resisting
with all her might.
[NAOFUMI]
And that was at Level 19.
Who knows how strong she'll
be at 70 or somethin'?
[ERHARDT]
So, you didn't come here
just to show off this
filolial queen, I assume?
We came to buy some clothing.
Clothing?
If she shreds them
each time she transforms,
I'll go broke in no time.
Please tell us that there's
some kind of outfit
made for transforming species.
Nah, those are
special order items.
I haven't got any of them.
Try going to see a dressmaker.
But I guess you can't have
her walking around in public
looking like that.
Take this. Another
customer left it.
[DRESSMAKER]
Oh, my god, she's cute!
Isn't she just the
cutest little angel?
Wait a second, she has
wings on her back,
so maybe she
really is an angel?
[RAPHTALIA chuckles]
Master, am I really
cute? I wanna know!
I don't know.
Fathers shouldn't
talk like that!
Father?!
Compliments are very
important to little girls,
helping them become even
cuter when they get older.
[NAOFUMI groans]
Then are you my father
or something else?
[NAOFUMI]
No, I'm your owner.
[FILO] I see.
Then what about Raphtalia?
[NAOFUMI]
She's kinda like my daughter.
I am not!
[NAOFUMI]
Anyway, that doesn't matter.
Why doesn't it matter?
We're just looking for clothes
that don't rip to shreds
when you transform and
then can go back to normal.
[DRESSMAKER] Ohh, that's
what you're looking for?
Did you bring any magic thread?
[NAOFUMI]
Magic thread?
[DRESSMAKER] Of course!
Transforming clothes always use
thread made out of
the wearer's own mana.
[RAPHTALIA] So transforming
clothes are always custom made?
[DRESSMAKER]
Of course!
If you will give me
the magic thread...
...I promise I'll make
you the cutest outfit
you'll ever see
in your entire life!
[FILO]
Huh?
[MAGIC SHOPKEEPER 5A]
Magic thread, huh?
You certainly could
weave them here,
but unfortunately right
now's not a good time.
I'm afraid the magic gemstone
in my spinning wheel broke.
[NAOFUMI]
Is it expensive?
It is, but the bigger problem
is that it's hard to find.
What can we do about it?
I'll talk to some people and see
if I can procure a new gemstone
as soon as possible.
It might take a
little bit longer.
--[FILO] Hey.
--[ALL] Huh?
Whoa, what does this thing do?
This crystal ball measures
one's magical affinity.
Why don't we measure
your affinity?
[NAOFUMI]
Oh, well. No outfit for a while.
[FILO]
♪ Filo has wind affinity! ♪
♪ I blow away all the enemies! ♪
Well, she's definitely
in a good mood.
[FILO]
♪ ...draw the carriage ♪
♪ to where my Master says! ♪
♪ If I find that
nasty spear guy, ♪
♪ I'll send him flying
with a full-power kick! ♪
[NAOFUMI]
It'll be a while before we can
get her some clothes.
In the meantime,
let's make some money.
[RAPHTALIA] This trade pass
we got from the village lord--
I hope it comes in handy soon.
Master, look, there's
someone up ahead.
--[MAN 6A panting]
--Is something wrong, sir?
[MAN 6A gasps]
Please, I beg you.
Give me a lift in your carriage.
Huh?
I need to get this
medicine to the village!
it's the one just
past the mountain.
It's urgent. I pray you!
Filo, how long to get
there at full speed?
Not too long.
But you know, we can
get there even sooner
without the carriage.
All right then, I'll take
you there for one silver.
Huh? I already... spent my
money on this medicine...
It doesn't matter how you do it.
Pay me now or you
can pay me later.
But just don't try
to worm out of it.
That would be fine, sir.
Right, give me
those reins, Raphtalia.
Here ya go.
[MAN 6A gasps]
Thank you.
You can save your thanks.
Just make sure you pay up.
Filo, let's go!
Righty-o!
[MAN 6A screams]
[GATEKEEPER 6A]
Halt! Stop!
You have to pay the toll!
--[NAOFUMI grunts]
--[GATEKEEPER 6A gasps]
I'll pick it up on the way back!
[MAN 6A]
Mother, I got you the medicine.
[coughs]
Listen, you go boil water.
I'll give the medicine
to your mother.
But I...
Relax, it's free.
[OLD WOMAN 6A coughs]
[OLD WOMAN 6A]
Thank you so much!
Mother!
The medicine--
it's helping already?
Yes, the pain went
away in an instant.
Thank you, good sir.
[MAN 6A] Um... exactly...
what kind of magic spell
did you use?
Trust me, it's better
you don't ask.
Now that that's done...
Oh, uh, here.
This should be worth
at least one silver.
Yeah, that'll do. See ya later.
Thank you very much.
Safe travels to you!
[NAOFUMI] Besides selling,
I could even transport people.
This travel trade might be more
profitable than I thought.
I really can't believe
I'm riding with
Our Savior of the Heavenly Fowl!
"Our Savior of
the Heavenly Fowl"?
Ah, yes. You have
quite the reputation.
"In a carriage drawn by the
god of domesticated birds,
Our Savior travels
and treats the sick!"
Did he just say I'm a god?
I'm surprised at you!
Didn't Master Naofumi tell you
not to talk when
there are strangers?
[FILO whines]
Sorry.
Well I'll be! It talks!
That really is a god!
No, she's not a god.
There's a large gang that's
blocking our path up ahead.
[NAOFUMI]
Mm?
Whoa, now! You can
stop right there!
Well that's an odd bird
you got there, stranger.
We heard an accessory seller
was hitchin' a ride with you.
Come on! We know
you're in there!
[gasps]
[NAOFUMI] I'll have to be more
careful choosing my clients.
Just hand him over quietly
and you'll get away with
at least your lives intact.
[NAOFUMI] Meaning you'll take
everything but our lives, right?
Ha, ha. This one's
sharp as tack, ain't he?
[BANDIT 6A] That one's
pretty hot, for a demi-human.
[BANDIT 6A laughs]
Looks like we're gonna
have some fun tonight!
[RAPHTALIA]
Master Naofumi,
may I have permission
to end his lineage?
Not that you'd listen
to me if I said no to you.
Me neither!
Don't even think about it.
We've got a class-upgraded
bodyguard who'll make
hamburger out of you.
It's all up to you now, Sensei!
[BODYGUARD 6A]
Hmph.
[NAOFUMI]
Class-upgraded?
There's another one
I haven't heard of.
Well, one thing's for sure: he's
not going to be easy pickings.
It'd sure be helpful
if I could come up with
some support magic now.
As source of thy
power, I order thee.
[NAOFUMI gasps]
Decipher the laws of nature
and conceal me utterly
in a magic haze.
Hide Mirage!
[BANDITS gasp]
Fast Tornado!
[BANDITS scream]
[BANDITS grumbling]
Some other trader told us to
mug the guy riding with you
because he was supposed
to be carrying a bunch of
really nice stuff!
I swear that's what happened!
So one of my own
sold me out, hmm?
Well, what do we do
with these guys now?
We usually hand them
over to the local guards,
but I'll leave it up to you.
Hey, you! You aren't
the Shield Hero, are ya?
Kinda obvious since ya have no
weapons and only that shield.
"We're just some
unlucky adventurers
who were attacked by
the cruel Shield Hero
and he treated all
of us like dirt!"
That what you're gonna
tell the guards?
You are the perceptive one.
Then you can bet
they'll take our word
over the Shield Hero's any day.
[BANDITS chuckle]
[sighs] I guess
I have no choice.
You have to die.
[BANDITS gasp]
[NAOFUMI]
Filo. You feel like a snack?
Yes, I do! I want food!
[BANDITS gasp]
[NAOFUMI]
See, she's an omnivore.
She'll gulp down
anything in one bite.
Hey, but you're Our Savior
of the Heavenly Fowl!
You can't commit murder!
[NAOFUMI]
I'm nobody's savior,
and I have to act with
my best interests in mind.
You guys must've killed
plenty of people so far.
Just consider this your
turn and give in to it.
No, wait, please!
Take anything you want, just
let us get out with our lives!
[NAOFUMI]
Got it.
I'll spare your lives, at least.
[BANDITS sigh]
[NAOFUMI]
However...
[BANDITS gasp]
[BANDITS grumbling]
[RAPHTALIA sighs] Are we
actually looting these bandits?
But doesn't this make us
just as evil as they are?
I'm afraid I don't agree.
They're offering up
everything they have
to purchase safe passage
from Our Savior.
He's simply treating
their lives as merchandise.
If I may say, Sir Hero's
a shining example
of the true trader's spirit--
something lacking in
our youth of today!
Looks like intimidation.
Hey, how 'bout the two of you
do a little less chatting
and a little more working?
And while we're on
the subject, pal,
how do you figure you're
going to compensate me
for the pack of trouble you
caused me on this trip?
[ACCESSORY DEALER 6A] I can
offer you all the knowledge
and connections I possess.
It is at your command.
Knowledge and connections?
Yes. I've taken a real
liking to you, Sir Hero.
[NAOFUMI]
Hmph.
[NAOFUMI] The first things
the accessory seller taught me
were how to process
precious metals,
use the tools required, craft
gems, and imbue them with mana.
[NAOFUMI] I even managed
to pick up some spells,
thanks to getting a feel
for this mana stuff.
And so, I started a new business
venture: crafting gemstones.
[NAOFUMI] Then I got an in
with the traders' grapevine,
where I heard rumors
of the other heroes.
Apparently, Motoyasu saved
a famine-stricken village
to the southwest by
introducing a legendary crop.
I bet that royal pain in the
butt came up with the idea.
Ren's apparently
moving southeast,
looking for monsters to slay.
I even heard a rumor that
he took down a dragon.
But the information regarding
Itsuki, the Bow Hero,
was all over the place.
Some said he's training
up in the mountains,
and some say he
went into a dungeon
on a quest for treasure.
There were even some tall tales,
like him joining another
country's resistance,
but in the end,
none of these wild stories
ended up being true.
That seller sure wasn't kidding
when he said he'd give us
knowledge and connections.
But one thing he offered helped
me more than anything else.
I can't believe it, but this
deed must be the real thing.
I'm amazed that
grumpy money-grubber
actually gave this to you.
Anyway, if there's
a gemstone you want,
I can arrange for
you to get it--
at a discount, of course, which
obviously goes without saying.
What are you
looking for, Sir Hero?
For the gemstone you used to
make threads that are magic.
[gasps]
What surprises me is
how you managed to
find that gemstone so quickly.
Well, it's not all
that simple, actually.
It's in a rather
unsavory location.
Master Naofumi.
Look.
[MAGIC SHOPKEEPER 5A]
A long time ago,
this temple was once a
notoriously evil alchemist's
base of operations.
Strange, though...
I'd never heard anything
about a tunnel being here.
[NAOFUMI]
According to the mining chief,
nobody's dared
approach this place
ever since monsters
started nesting here.
Keep your eyes peeled.
[RAPHTALIA]
It's empty.
[MAGIC SHOPKEEPER 5A]
Ancient writing.
"We fervently pray
that this seed
never makes it
out of this tunnel.
It is a horribly twisted
manifestation of our wish
that nobody feel
the pangs of hunger
ever again in this world."
[NAOFUMI]
Well, it looks like some bandits
may have already released it.
Master, look down there.
There's a path over that way.
[NAOFUMI]
Let's go.
Uhh--
[NAOFUMI] Hey, Filo! What
are you doing? Hurry up!
Um, Master, I think
you should really, um...
--[NAOFUMI] For cryin' out loud.
--[FILO gasps]
If you won't listen to me,
then I don't need you anymore.
[gasps]
Stop here.
What is it?
A monster footprint.
And my goodness,
but it's a large one.
Anyway.
We're gonna have to keep going
until we get what we came for.
Just remember to be c--
--[FILO gasps]
--Master Naofumi?!
[NAOFUMI]
Just stay calm!
Hey, witch. What's going on?
[RAPHTALIA] I'm sick and tired
of being Master Naofumi's slave.
[gasps]
[RAPHTALIA] I only pretended
to become his slave again
to kill him with my own hands.
I can stab him clean
through from behind now.
[NAOFUMI gasps]
[MAGIC SHOPKEEPER 5A] Don't
let the voices mislead you!
[NAOFUMI]
What are they?
The monsters provoke you.
They do it by saying the
last things you want to hear,
in the last voices
you want saying them!
[NAOFUMI]
How nasty is that?
[FILO]
Master is my lunch!
[groans]
Hey, something cut me!
Do something about this!
As source of thy power,
I order thee.
Decipher the laws of nature
and restore our sight!
Fast Anti-Bind right now!
If we can see them... Filo!
I'm on it!
I'm gonna blow you away!
Well then, are you okay?
Yes, I'm fine, thank you.
[NAOFUMI] I don't see how
that's going to come in handy.
Let's keep going now.
Excuse me, Master?
You won't abandon
Filo, will you?
I've got money riding on you.
I'm not gonna get rid
of you that easily.
Master Naofumi...
Stop worrying, Filo.
Master Naofumi would
never say any mean things
like those hallucinations
you heard. Count on it!
[FILO]
Mm. All right.
Huh?
Uh, forget it. It's nothing.
Something's there.
[MAGIC SHOPKEEPER 5A]
Hmm?
That's it.
Yeah... But, uh...
[hisses]
That's a nue.
A little on the smaller side,
but still dangerous.
This might be rough.
The gemstone is right
there in front of us
and we can't get at it.
Let's go!
[NAOFUMI gasps]
Oh, those two. Cover us, please!
[yells]
[RAPHTALIA gasps, groans]
Zweit Fire Blast!
--[NUE roars]
--[NAOFUMI grunts]
Master Naofumi!
[NAOFUMI]
Can I hold it off?
[FILO]
Don't!
[NAOFUMI gasps]
Hey!
[roars]
[NAOFUMI gasps]
That was close...
We need to avoid that
lightning at all costs.
But then...
how can we attack it?
[gasps]
--[footsteps]
--[NUE growls]
Raphtalia! Look out!
How could it see
her from behind?
Well it didn't see her,
it heard her.
It's really sensitive to sound.
To sound...
[roars]
Filo! Yell into this thing
as loudly as you can!
Okay!
[NAOFUMI]
Cover your ears--quick!
[yells]
Kill it, now!
Zweit Fire Blast!
[yells]
[FILO grunts]
[roars]
[FILO]
We won!
[NAOFUMI]
Are you okay?
[FILO]
Mm-hmm.
And how about you?
[NAOFUMI]
Yeah, I'm fine.
Don't be so reckless next time.
[RAPHTALIA]
But, uh...
[NAOFUMI] What if you
were seriously hurt?
You could have been
scarred for life.
You mean you're
worried I could've--
Got it?
Uh, yes.
[FILO]
Wow, so pretty!
They're so beautiful!
[thud]
[FILO groans, whines]
Doing this is making
me feel so tired.
Don't worry, my dear,
it's only because your mana
is turning into thread.
Endure it for just
a while longer.
What?
[RAPHTALIA] I'll give you some
nice snacks once you finish.
[FILO]
Yummy ones?
Then I'll keep going!
Oh!
[RAPHTALIA groans]
Well, how do I look? All right?
You look terrific.
[FILO]
Yay! Thank you, Master!
I mean, sure, she looks
cute and everything--
--She's darling!
--[NAOFUMI] Huh?
I did my very best to
bring out every last bit
of Filo's angelic charm and
I think I did a hell of a job!
I used white as the base color,
to go with her wings,
and I added plenty of frills
as a nod to her feathers, too.
And since it would contrast best
with her lovely blonde hair,
I went with blue for
the ribbon, as you can see.
Sure, right.
Well now, that magic outfit
and the monster crest
add up to, um...
340 silvers, I guess.
You're gonna have to
work hard to pay it off.
Yay! I'll do my best!
[RAPHTALIA gasps] Don't
suddenly transform indoors!
Huh?
[DRESSMAKER squeals]
Even on a monster, it's cute!
--[NAOFUMI gasps]
--I'm sure you agree, don't you?
Isn't your daughter
cute as a button?!
[NAOFUMI]
She's not my daughter!