So return to--
[NAOFUMI]
What the hell are you doing?!
Curse you!
How dare you take the royal
Princess Melty hostage!
I'm not taking anybody hostage!
You're a liar!
Fellow knights, justice is ours!
Let's destroy this
Devil of the Shield!
[KNIGHTS yell]
Terrific, so now
I've become a devil, huh?
Raphtalia! Filo!
[yells]
[giggles]
Full retreat!
[KNIGHTS yell]
[KNIGHT 13A]
Run away!
Can we chase them down?
Nah.
Mel, are you hurt anywhere?
Now or Never
Just fight it out
Night sky reflects in my eyes
Holdin' up my hand to the stars
All the time is nearing
future's bleeding
But I want to be
honest with myself
Come clean Follow the wind (ah?)
I'm gonna make a scene
Keep it real, make a mark (ah?)
on the masterpiece
Everybody betray me
Touch of your hand
brushed me softly
Everything betray me
Shake all you want
But this feeling won't die
Through hundreds of times
through millions of times
I'm adding up scars
never giving up my faith
It' s proof I'm alive now,
always be myself
I gotta make a change
(make a change yeah)
In this distorted world
I follow the footsteps
Holding back screaming
everything is silent
Through hundreds of times
through millions of times
I Find & Create myself
Now or Never
Just fight it out
[FILO]
Mel, uhm...
[rustling]
[RAPHTALIA]
Master Naofumi.
[NAOFUMI]
How'd it go?
The altered images
have made their way
to almost all the nearby
towns and villages.
Entering them
would be too risky.
I see...
[RAPHTALIA]
Wait, isn't that...
What was the point
of trying to kill
the second princess
right in front of us?
[KNIGHT 13A]
Hmph.
Y'hear what I said?!
I have nothing
to say to the devil,
so you can kill me now!
That's a rosary from
the Three Heroes Church.
Wait, the Three Heroes Church?
They worship the Sword,
Spear, and Bow Heroes.
It's Melromarc's state religion.
That's weird, I saw one of these
at the church
in the capital, too.
Yeah, all the heroes
except the shield, huh?
[KNIGHT 13A]
You will pay the price
of disturbing
the natural order!
And you'll suffer for it!!
[RAPHTALIA]
What was he talking about?
Y'got me, Raphtalia.
One of the king's
harebrained ideas.
And thanks to the
stupidity of her father,
we're stuck here
with nowhere to go.
[MELTY]
My father can't be behind this.
Yeah, right, and who else
could've ordered
something like that?
My sister, probably.
So she's trying to kill
you and take your place
as crown princess,
is that what you're saying?
[MELTY]
Mm.
[NAOFUMI]
But I know that those knights
who attacked us are under
the king's direct control.
It'd be natural to assume he's
in the middle of everything.
If I'm right, those guys--
there's nothing they'd
love more than to frame
the mythical "Devil of the
Shield" for this whole thing.
[MELTY] Father would never
stoop to something so low!
What makes you so sure, kid?
[MELTY]
Because... Because Father is...
I don't know how you
can stick up for him.
That scumbag...
But you're wrong.
How so?
You're totally wrong!
Why can't either
of you understand?
We don't have time
to fight each other,
there are problems before us
we need to solve together!
Please!
Talk to Father one
more time, I beg you!
[RAPHTALIA]
Master Naofumi...
I can't...
How will I ever
face Mother like this?!
I just can't do it!
You don't have to cry, Mel.
I'm still here for you.
[MELTY sobbing]
We're out of time.
[FILO]
Master.
Welcome back.
[MELTY]
Hmph!
[NAOFUMI]
Listen.
We're going to have
to leave the country.
So what'll you do?
I'll return to the
capital somehow.
I have to talk to Father and--
--[NAOFUMI] Lousy idea.
--[gasps]
[NAOFUMI] You go back now,
you'd only get yourself killed.
However, if you were to change
your mind and stay with us,
I'll keep you safe.
I can promise you that,
if nothing else.
Oh, come with us, please.
All right.
[NAOFUMI]
We'll leave before dawn.
Make sure you're ready.
Master Naofumi,
where are we going to
be traveling this time?
Don't worry,
I'll let you know...
What about the wagon?
Come on, you knew the deal.
There's no way we could
cross this range on a wagon.
We'll come back for it
once this thing's over.
[FILO]
Promise?
You promise
we'll come back for it?
[NAOFUMI]
I promise.
Let's take
a little break in here.
Okay!
[NAOFUMI]
You all right, Princess?
Fine, thank you.
She must be
tired after everything.
Master Naofumi,
why did you choose
the kingdom of Siltvelt over
all the other possibilities?
The extra security.
There's gotta be a really good
reason they're trying so hard
to prevent us
from getting there.
It might just be the
perfect place to hide out.
Ah! Right!
[MELTY]
Father...
There's something I need
to ask you, Sir Shield Hero.
What happened
between you and Father?
[MELTY]
I mean, my mother said
that the Shield Hero
should be treated well.
What happened?
Come to think of it,
now that you mention it,
I don't know a single
thing about your mom.
What's to say?
She's the queen of
the country of Melromarc.
Queen, huh?
Yes, that means
she's higher than Father
in the pecking order.
Wait, how come the queen's
more powerful than the king?
Melromarc is a country
based on matrilineal succession.
Gimme a break!
You mean the king married
into the royal family?
What's so funny about that?
Nothing except for the fact that
he acts like he runs the joint.
[MELTY]
Well, he is the king, after all!
So he's like adopted royalty?
[RAPHTALIA gasps]
[NAOFUMI]
Time to go.
[KNIGHT 13G]
They're not over here.
[KNIGHT 13H]
They can't have gone far.
Find them!
[KNIGHTS chattering]
They've blocked
this route off, too.
We'll have to find another path.
[MELTY screams]
[KNIGHT 13I]
There they are! Down there!
Looks like we're
gonna have company.
Can you run?
I think.
[NAOFUMI] We'll make a break
for it past that big rock!
[KNIGHTS shouting]
That's it, you've got
nowhere left to run.
You're surrounded.
Even you have to admit that.
Cease your resistance and
release Princess Melty at once.
What's with this
"release" business?
It's not like I have
her tied up or anything.
Quit lying to us.
We have all the
proof we need now.
Please, Sir Heroes.
I'm perfectly fine,
as you can well see.
The Shield Hero kept watch
over me, making sure I was safe.
Wait a minute.
This whole thing is happening
because Naofumi abducted you.
This is all a misunderstanding.
You see, someone is
plotting to have me killed.
I asked him to take me with
him and to protect my life.
He's protecting you? Come on!
[MELTY] What advantage could
the Shield Hero possibly stand
to gain by abducting me?
The queen told me
this is the time for all
of us to work together.
It's the only way we'll be able
to thwart the catastrophes.
Our world can't
withstand any more
of these ridiculous,
pointless conflicts!
Put your weapons away, please!
Like she says, this whole thing
was a setup from the beginning.
I have no secrets.
I'll tell you everything
I know. And then--
[MYNE] I command you
not to listen to him!
That lying devil possesses
a brainwashing shield!
It allows him take over your
mind by simply talking to you--
it's the most dangerous
weapon he has!
Wha...?
Who would believe something
so stupid and silly?!
The Three Heroes Church
has discovered that heretics
who worship the Shield have
started popping up all over
the kingdom in the past month.
The Three Heroes Church again?
The Devil of the Shield
calls himself
"the Savior of
the Heavenly Fowl"
and goes around
brainwashing the innocent!
Sister, you're mad!
Melty, my dear, little,
deranged creature!
It's obvious that
Devil of the Shield
has already brainwashed you.
Now I see!
That means that
Raphtalia and Filo
were brainwashed
by Naofumi, too.
No, you're wrong!
Master Naofumi hasn't
brainwashed any of us!
If my shield really
had the ability to do that,
we wouldn't be in this damned
situation in the first place!
Do we have a
guarantee that it can't?
What kind of proof can
you give to convince us
that you're not lying?
Naofumi, hand over
the princess right now,
and no one'll get hurt.
I promise you she won't
be harmed in any way.
[gasps]
You know, if we can
avoid all this fighting,
I guess it might
be for the best.
[MYNE] You are
absolutely right, Sir Ren!
I'm so glad we all agree that
Melty's safety comes first!
[gasps]
Come.
Let's all go home together now.
No...
If I go, I'll be killed!
[MYNE] Come to me,
dearest little sister.
Please, Sir Hero!
Please help!
Y'know, Ren, I have to admit
that your offer is generous,
but I just do not trust that
woman with the princess.
What are you suggesting?
[RAPHTALIA gasps]
[inaudible]
What's that devil
talking about now?
Melty is my
dearest little sister,
I wouldn't dream of anything--
Come off it, lady,
you're not fooling anyone.
You want to be crown
princess so badly
you'd kill your own sister!
You'll say you're undoing
the "brainwashing"
and then kill her
when nobody's looking.
I'll bet that's exactly
what you're planning!
Don't forget, I promised
to keep you safe.
Filo, now!
'Kay!
Ready when you are!
[MYNE yelps]
Air Strike Shield now!
Not so fast!
[ALL screaming]
[NAOFUMI gasps]
I've called for backup,
so it's too late for
you to try to escape.
I can't get this off.
It's... Huh?
--[shrieks]
--You're finally mine, Filo!
Let go of me, help!
I've lost all my strength!
--Please let go of me!
--I had the royal alchemists
come up with this
ankle bracelet for ya.
So now you're gonna stay my
little angel forever and ever!
[MELTY] As source of
thy power, I order thee.
Decipher the laws of
nature and slice through
my target like a blade of water.
Zweit Aqua Slash!
Let her go!
I'm not gonna miss next time!
Myne, wait a sec!
Are you trying to kill
your sister Melty?!
I have to defend myself
since she attacked first!
Zweit Hellfire!
Zweit Fire Arrow!
What are you doing?!
Stop now!
To save her from Naofumi's
brainwashing, she must die!
Master Naofumi...
Can I leave Mel with you
for a bit? I'll be right back.
[NAOFUMI]
Sure.
Step back a little.
All right...
Come forth, Rage Shield!
Here I come, Filo... [giggles]
Huh?
[NAOFUMI yelling]
What's with the shield?
Bring down the hammer of justice
on the Devil of the Shield!
Archers, fire!
[gasps]
Not on my watch.
It's my turn now!
[yells]
Annihilate the Devil of the
Shield and his whole party!
[KNIGHTS yelling]
[REN]
Wait, don't!
[KNIGHTS yelling]
[KNIGHTS scream]
That light, what is it?
[REN]
What the hell's going on?
[NAOFUMI]
Ren...
I know you'll be able
to figure this all out--
what's really happening here.
Wait, Naofumi!
[FILO]
Yay!
[rustling]
[MELTY]
Wait!
She's on our side.
That's one of the Shadows,
an espionage squad under
the queen's direct control.
Sir Shield Hero,
this is the first time
I'm meeting you
in this form, I daresay.
"Daresay." What's that about?
[SHADOW] Allow me to
get straight to the point.
Sir Shield Hero, you are
hereby requested to meet with
Her Majesty the Queen.
With the queen?
The roots of this commotion
go deep, you understand?
I daresay we would appreciate
all the help you can give.
This abduction and the events
leading up to it were set up
by those who find your
accomplishments alarming.
Oh, that's terrific,
more pains in the
butt to deal handle.
Yeah? So?
What would I gain
by meeting with her?
I have no doubt you'll
understand better
after you've met, I daresay.
[NAOFUMI] The queen's
in the opposite direction
from Siltvelt.
Hey, Second Princess, you know
anything about this country?
Oh, yeah, Second Princess.
You know how to
use magic, don't you?
[MELTY]
Don't call me that.
[NAOFUMI]
What was that, Second Princess?
Stop calling me Second Princess!
What's gotten into
you all of a sudden?
I have a name,
and it's Melty, that's what!
Why on earth do
you keep calling me
"Second Princess," Shield Hero?
You keep treating me like
I'm just an outsider!
Hey, you're the only
one around here
calling me "Shield
Hero," y'know.
Well then... I'll have
to call you Naofumi.
And you can call me Melty,
which is what I prefer anyway.
So tell me, Naofumi,
what's it going to be?
Straight to his first name?
Well, Second Princess,
y'see, it's like this...
--Hey, wait!
--[NAOFUMI] Okay.
[NAOFUMI]
Melty.
Happy now?
Once again, please...
Huh?
[MELTY]
Say my name one more time.
Fine, Melty.
Good. And I suggest
you don't forget it, either.
One more thing...
Thanks for that.
[NAOFUMI]
Hmm? What's up?
Nothing!
I'm fine, just forget it.
[gasps]
Where's that smell coming from?
[MYNE giggling]