[MIRELIA] Is that what
the king has been up to?
He has, apparently.
I'm sure Princess Malty
must've talked him into it.
[MIRELIA] How is the
Shield Hero holding up?
He procured a demi-human girl
from a slave trader a while ago.
[MIRELIA]
Is that so?
Well, that's a
relief, I must say.
However...
News of Melromarc's summoning
of the Four Cardinal Heroes
is making no small impact in
our kingdom as well as others.
We must make sure we
prevent our neighbors
from meddling in our affairs,
no matter what it may take.
Never fear, my lady.
We'll continue to
keep a watchful eye
on events in the capital.
[MIRELIA]
I'm counting on you.
[AULTCRAY] As a reward for
his efforts during the Wave
and for fulfilling my request,
Master Motoyasu will
receive 4,000 silvers.
And Young Masters Itsuki and
Ren will receive 3,800 silvers.
Finally, I have set aside 500
silvers for the Shield Hero.
--However...
--Huh?
Since it's been offset
by the cost of
setting his slave
free from her curse,
he will not receive
any funds at this time.
[NAOFUMI grunts]
[ITSUKI] Wait a second,
that's not gonna fly.
[RAPHTALIA, NAOFUMI gasp]
You were the one interfering
in his duel, dispelling that...
...slave crest,
or whatever you call it.
Now you won't pay him?
If you ask me,
that's not really fair play.
Yeah, that's right.
If you'd followed the rules,
Naofumi clearly
would've won the duel.
Wha-- Are you crazy?
I didn't lose!
I'm afraid you're both mistaken,
Sir Itsuki, Sir Ren.
It was supposed to be
a one-on-one duel,
and the Shield Hero was
the one with monsters
hidden inside his cape.
That is the real reason
why Father didn't
declare him the winner.
[ITSUKI] Even so, you cheated
by firing a magic spell at him.
[MOTOYASU gasps]
Get off of me!
[NAOFUMI] Might as well,
since I'm a cowardly cheater!
[NAOFUMI gasps, groans]
[REN]
Besides, when the Wave hit,
it was Naofumi who defended
that village, not the knights.
So if you ask me,
it would be the right thing
to fairly compensate him.
[MYNE grunts]
Fine. I shall afford him
the minimum agreed amount,
but there will be nothing else.
[AULTCRAY] Well, you have it,
so begone already!
[growls]
[RAPHTALIA]
Master Naofumi!
Isn't it great?
[RAPHTALIA] There's no reason
for us to waste any more
of our precious time here.
Hm?
C'mon, Raphtalia, let's go.
[RAPHTALIA giggles]
In this empty void I
found the way to the light
Can't find my way
in this lingering world
Searching for the answer
the one that I can trust in
I'm just wandering around
Yeah, still stuck
in the shadow, ay
But I never follow that
This pain at last
Soon will pass
Turn into my own
unbeatable strength
This guy or that guy
dead or alive
by hiding alone we can't survive
I don't want to lie to myself
Keep on the fight, get right
I'll never lose and cry
Keep run up day and night
Time to rewrite
No matter what anyone say
I find my way, yeah
Never go away
Now, Nobody can stop me no way
I will make sure not to
forget those precious things
Yeah I'll take a stand
get back all that I've lost
Rise suddenly in this world
(I don't look back yeah)
This repetition will
repeat till the end
And the regrets are
still lingering in my head
Time to get it all back
now turn over
Rise suddenly in this world
(I don't look back yeah)
--[sizzling]
--[RAPHTALIA groans]
[SLAVE TRADER]
There we go!
She now has one
brand-new slave crest.
[NAOFUMI] There was no need
to get another one, you know.
But I wanted it.
I think of it as a symbol
of your faith in me,
Master Naofumi.
All right, suit yourself.
[RAPHTALIA]
A-Anyway, uh...
So, um... how do you
think it looks?
Slave User's Shield, huh?
Uh, what was that?
Never mind, nothing at all!
[SLAVE TRADER]
I'm amazed.
You've helped this
scrawny bag of bones
grow so much in such
a short span of time.
You could get 20 for her
if she was a virgin!
But I am a virgin!
--Thirty-five gold pieces!
--[RAPHTALIA gasps]
Wow, 35 gold pieces.
[RAPHTALIA]
Master Naofumi!
[SLAVE TRADER]
Huh?
[NAOFUMI]
Hm?
What's that?
This is a monster egg lottery.
For a hundred silvers, you're
guaranteed at least a filolial!
You'll win a monster chick
that'll double in value
if ya take care of it properly.
A filolial?
[RAPHTALIA]
Certainly.
You surely must have
seen them around.
They're those gigantic
birds everywhere
that pull people's
carriages around town.
[NAOFUMI]
Oh, those?
What's more, if ya
hit the jackpot...
...you'll win a dragon!
And may I remind you that
beast is worth 20 gold pieces!
Is it like a gacha game?
[RAPHTALIA]
What's a gacha game?
Nothing. Just forget I said it.
[SLAVE TRADER] So, would you
like to give it a shot?
Act now and I'll give ya
a package deal, sir!
For that and the slave crest!
[RAPHTALIA]
If you ask me,
you shouldn't waste money
like that, Master Naofumi.
Yeah, but after
thinking about it,
I figured it wasn't fair to
make you fight all by yourself.
At least this way,
you can have a monster
that'll fight by your side.
I fight just fine
all by myself!
[NAOFUMI]
If that's the case,
we can always sell it back
to the slave merchant.
Well, either way,
you'd better stop
loosening your purse
strings so much.
[NAOFUMI]
Yeah, yeah, fine.
[HERBALIST 1A] I have lots of
relatives in Lute Village.
They're the ones who asked
me to help you out here.
Do you think it might have been
someone you saved back then?
You got me.
[HERBALIST 1A] This grimoire
has recipes for finer medicines
than the ones you bring me.
Use it. It's yours.
[NAOFUMI] Thanks, but I can't
read this world's language.
There's something else.
The old hag at the magic shop
was asking to see you.
It's for a similar reason.
She said you helped her grandkid
out in that Lute Village battle.
[MAGIC SHOPKEEPER 5A]
You have a rare affinity
for healing and
support magic, Shield Hero.
And the young lady
has affinities
for light and dark magic.
She's half-raccoon, after all.
Make sure she learns
illusion magic.
[MAGIC SHOPKEEPER 5A]
Now, that being the case...
We don't have the money to
buy a magic grimoire, though.
It's a gift, as thanks
for helping my grandchild.
I would've preferred to have
given you a crystal ball
instead of it.
Huh?
[MAGIC SHOPKEEPER 5A] Oh,
you mean you didn't you know?
If you use a crystal ball,
you can learn one of the
magics sealed within it.
[NAOFUMI]
First I ever heard of that.
But I heard the royal court
had ordered a bunch of them
to give to all the heroes.
[NAOFUMI]
Yeah, they probably did.
To every hero but me, that is.
Learning magic from a
grimoire is certainly hard.
But if you keep at
it and do the work,
you can learn as many
spells as you want!
You can do it!
Thank you so much.
[NAOFUMI gasps]
[NAOFUMI]
"Thank you so much"?
I really can't read it.
I wish there was
some kind of skill
that would translate
books for me.
[RAPHTALIA]
Then let's learn it together.
The language and the magic?
[RAPHTALIA]
Well, yes, actually.
But the key word
there is "together"!
Well, since the next Wave
isn't due for another month,
I guess that's the plan.
Let's spend the night
down in Lute Village.
Then tomorrow, after breakfast,
we can go out and
grind some levels.
Sure thing!
[NAOFUMI]
Hey, wake up!
Raphtalia!
[RAPHTALIA groans]
Piyo!
[BOTH gasp]
Pi!
It's so cute, Master Naofumi!
Pi, pi, pi, pi!
[RAPHTALIA giggles]
It must think you're its mother.
[NAOFUMI]
Yeah. Imprinting, huh?
[RAPHTALIA] We need to
think of a good name for it.
[NAOFUMI]
Oh, boy...
[RAPHTALIA] I can't believe she
grew so much in just two days!
My Growth Boost skill
probably helped a little.
Right, Filo?
Gua.
[RAPHTALIA] You named her
Filo as in "filolial"?
Um...
Don't you think that's
a little bit obvious?
Yeah, but she seems
to really like it.
Gua!
[VILLAGER 5A]
Hey, look at that.
[VILLAGER 5B]
Why are the knights here?
Huh?
[MYNE] In light of his
exploits during the last Wave,
the Spear Hero, Sir Motoyasu,
has been appointed ruling
lord of this region.
[VILLAGERS murmuring]
To help the rebuilding efforts,
we've decided to levy a toll.
This toll will be 50 silvers
to enter the village
and 50 to exit.
But that'll ruin us!
We won't have anything left
to buy food tomorrow!
Do you dare to defy
your lord's orders?
[NAOFUMI]
Yep, you bet!
[MYNE, VILLAGERS gasp]
[MYNE]
Ugh, the Shield Hero?
What are you still doing here?
This is Sir Motoyasu's
domain now.
You have no right
to question him.
Actually, leave this instant,
you miserable criminal!
[groans] Oh, don't worry,
I'm glad to leave.
But, you know,
I don't think the villagers
will be too happy about it.
Motoyasu!
You have any idea
how much it costs
to spend a night
at the inn here?
Huh? Actually, um...
One silver a night,
with food included.
You're charging the
equivalent of a hundred nights
just to enter and exit the
village, do you realize that?
[VILLAGER 5A]
Yeah, yeah!
[VILLAGER 5B]
He's right!
And you can't just show up here
and call yourself our lord.
And it was the Shield Hero who
defended this whole village
when the Wave of
Catastrophe hit!
You dare complain
about a royal decree?!
[VILLAGERS gasp]
I suggest you all knock it off!
[gasps]
I trust you know who we
represent, Princess Malty.
But why have you come?
For you.
Master Naofumi, who are they?
I haven't a clue, but they're
important, that's for sure.
How could this be?! [groans]
Shield Hero!
Fight us for the right
to rule this village.
[RAPHTALIA, NAOFUMI]
Huh?
I decline!
But sir, if you
refuse this challenge,
the village will fall into
the Spear Hero's hands!
Though it pains me to admit it,
not even I, as the lord,
can accept further taxation!
But why do I have to
ride in a dragon race?
Sounds like nothin' but
a pain in the butt.
But they've specifically
asked for you, Shield Hero.
As a result, we don't
have any right
to challenge a Cardinal Hero.
Know what I think?
I'd bet anything
it was that message
that bent Myne out of shape.
Do you... Do you mean
she's taking it out on you?
--[FILO] Gua! Gu!
--[BOTH] Hm?
[LORD 3A] Your filolial
certainly appears to be
up for it.
[NAOFUMI]
What's her problem?
It sure looks like it's true
that filolials and dragons
don't get along
very well together.
Please, we're begging you!
We'll give you a huge reward for
winning if you accept for us!
[sighs]
I just can't make any
guarantees that I'll win.
[MOTOYASU]
That is so lame.
You're gonna ride that
bird thing? Not a dragon?
How can you possibly keep up
with my dragon with that thing?
[FILO grunts]
[MOTOYASU groans]
--[KNIGHTS gasp]
--[MYNE shrieks]
Sir Motoyasu!
[groans]
[MYNE]
Sir Motoyasu!
Healing magic! C'mon!
[SOLDIER 5A]
Right away!
[NAOFUMI]
Hmph.
[MYNE]
You cheater!
[NAOFUMI] It's his fault
for gettin' too close.
[gasps]
[BOTH laughing]
[RAPHTALIA]
I've never seen Master Naofumi
laugh so much before.
It suits him.
[LORD 3A]
The race will be three laps
around the outskirts
of the village.
Whoever reaches this gate first
will be declared the winner.
[MYNE]
Sir Motoyasu!
Master Naofumi!
Good luck, you can do it!
[LORD 3A]
On your marks...
Go!
[MOTOYASU grunts]
This'll be a piece of cake.
Gua!
[MOTOYASU coughs]
As source of thy
power, I order thee.
Decipher the laws of nature and
create a pit in front of me.
[SOLDIER 5B]
Earth Hole!
[gasps]
[VILLAGER 5A]
No! The Shield Hero!
[MYNE]
Hmph.
Poor Filo!
Sir Motoyasu!
Keep it up. Doing great!
[gasps] Huh?
[VILLAGERS cheering]
[SOLDIER 5A] As source of
thy power, I order thee.
Decipher the laws of nature
and hear my command
to slow my target.
Speed Down!
[NAOFUMI gasps]
--[FILO groans]
--How's that?!
Damn it!
Gua!
Huh?
[gasps]
[MOTOYASU groans]
What are you doing?
Run faster, damn it!
[MOTOYASU gasps]
[VILLAGERS cheering]
[MYNE gasps]
Filo! You've only got
one last lap to go!
[MYNE coughs, groans]
Foul beast!
Decipher the laws of nature
and heed my command
to hasten my target.
Fast Speed!
[gasps]
[NAOFUMI]
He's blocking my path!
We're headed straight
for the hole!
[NAOFUMI]
Let's do this, Filo!
Now! Air Strike Shield!
[FILO]
Gua!
[MOTOYASU gasps]
[VILLAGERS cheering]
Master Naofumi!
Hang in there, Shield Hero!
Push it faster!
[VILLAGER 5C] Don't let him
beat you! Keep running!
[NAOFUMI, MOTOYASU grunting]
[VILLAGERS cheer]
I suppose... I guess we won.
[VILLAGERS chattering]
Brilliantly done!
Thanks to you, we can rest easy
and focus on
rebuilding the village!
[BOTH gasp]
If you wanna thank
someone, thank Filo here.
Mm--huh?
Gua!
[NAOFUMI gasps]
[MYNE]
You cheated!
You didn't tell us your
filolial was really
this massive tub of lard I see!
[LORD 3A]
But it only transformed
after the race was over.
If anyone cheated,
it was you guys!
What about the
holes in the road?
Holes? Don't be ridiculous.
[BLACK-CLAD WOMAN 5A]
The Shield Hero is correct.
[MYNE gasps]
[BLACK-CLAD WOMAN 5A]
We have detected traces of magic
on the course.
It was--
Look at him!
It was obviously that criminal
who used illegal magic.
Untrue. The Shield
Hero's magic affinities
are support and healing.
His raccoon friend's
are light and dark.
Both are completely different
types than the magic we found.
[NAOFUMI] When did they
learn so much about us?
[BLACK-CLAD WOMAN 5A]
Thus it is clear that
the Spear Hero's party cheated.
Well, we'll leave for now!
But we'll be back.
You can count on it!
[MOTOYASU]
Remember, I let you win today,
but it won't happen next time!
And you won't have
that fat tub of--
Hey now, how's
your crotch doin'?
[RAPHTALIA gasps]
Master Naofumi!
[MOTOYASU growls] Well--you--
Anyway, I'll get you yet!
[RAPHTALIA]
Uh... Feel better.
[MOTOYASU groaning]
Sir Hero. Again, the whole
village thanks you so very much.
We don't know how to
express our gratitude
for everything you've done.
Forget about that.
Just lemme have the reward.
Sir, we're--we're going
around the village
collecting money right now.
Please give us a
few more days to--
[NAOFUMI]
I don't want money.
Huh?
--[VILLAGERS gasp]
-- Sir Hero!
I sure don't want
any rumors spreading
about how I took all
your rebuilding funds
and didn't leave
you with anything.
Nobody in this village
would ever say such a thing!
[NAOFUMI sighs]
You think not?
[LORD 3A]
But then, Sir Hero,
how else can we
properly reward you?
[FILO grunts]
Huh?
Gua.
[LORD 3A]
Huh?
Huh? Oh!
[FILO]
Gua!
Gua, gua, gua!
[RAPHTALIA] S-Sorry,
Master Naofumi, but, um...
...could we stop for
a little bit, just for a second?
--[NAOFUMI] Huh?
--[RAPHTALIA gags]
[RAPHTALIA retches]
[NAOFUMI]
Uck...
I'm sorry about this--
to make you work after
you let me rest all day.
We're gonna be traveling
a lot by cart now.
You need to find a way to
get over your motion sickness.
I'll try.
[NAOFUMI]
Your face is a little red.
You have a fever?
No, I don't.
[RAPHTALIA] Filo looks happy now
that she gets to pull a cart.
She sure does.
Gua!
Are you interested in becoming
a traveling trader, Sir Hero?
A trader?
If you are, this pass
will come in handy.
It exempts you from paying
tolls across the country,
so you'll be free to travel
the roads wherever you wish.
Now we can run a
traveling business
while fighting monsters
and leveling up.
That's not too bad.
[RAPHTALIA]
I'll do my best, too.
Get some sleep for tonight.
I'm not tired so
I'll keep watch.
Oh. All right.
[FILO]
Gua...
Filo!
[NAOFUMI] Your feathers
are stuffy as hell,
you realize that?
[FILO]
Meanie!
[RAPHTALIA]
Master Naofumi.
Master Naofumi!
[NAOFUMI groans]
[RAPHTALIA gasping]
Whoa... I'm sorry.
I guess I must've fallen asleep.
[FILO groans]
[gasps]
[NAOFUMI]
Huh?
[FILO groans]
[gasps]
That--That girl is--
Master, hi!
Good morning!
Uhh--?!
[RAPHTALIA]
Who the heck is she?!
How would I know?!
[FILO]
Huh?
Can I have something to eat?