You have visitors.
I apologize.
What the hell do you want?
Please let us accompany you!
At least during the Waves!
[NAOFUMI] Can you arrange
a class upgrade for us?
[SLAVE TRADER]
You can still get it done
by simply applying
at any other country's
dragon hourglass.
[NAOFUMI]
We won't be able to get there
before the next Wave.
[RAPHTALIA] Once all the
Waves have been repelled,
you'll probably go back--
back to your home world,
and I'll never see you again.
[MIRELIA]
The Wave's nearly here.
[exhales] Can we hold it?
It's almost that time.
Along with the potions,
I threw in some leftover
weapons I had laying around.
They'll make for decent backups.
[RAPHTALIA]
Thank you so much.
Still, I'm pretty
impressed you were able
to stock up on so much
medicine in so little time.
This still might not be enough.
There's no way we can tell
what'll happen during the Wave.
[ERHARDT laughs]
If you're being that careful,
you won't have to worry at all.
[NAOFUMI]
Oh, right.
Hold out your hand, Raphtalia.
All right...
Um, what's that?
[NAOFUMI] It's got a spell to
boost your mana generation.
Helluva present for a lady...
Boost my mana generation?
Will it really?!
I'm so happy! Thank you!
Huh?
How come she's the only
one who gets a present?
She isn't, check this out.
[FILO gasps]
It'll make your
speed and agility
twice what it was.
It's cute, Filo. You like it?
[FILO]
Do I like it?! Are you kidding?!
Thank you, Master! Yay!
[NAOFUMI]
And a hairpin won't fall off
when you transform.
What's brought on this
accessory-making spree?
Did some rich eccentric
uncle leave you
his fortune or what?
It'll help 'em boost
their stats, that's all.
Right...
[AKE]
The time has come.
Get yourselves
together because
you'll be teleported with me.
Yes, sir!
[NAOFUMI]
Okay, It's time.
Here we go...
Be right back!
[chuckles] I'll be
waiting in the shop!
You just come back alive!
[ALL panting]
[screaming]
Everyone else in the village
has already evacuated!
Get out of here now!
[VILLAGER 11A]
R-Right! Yes, sir!
I think he's the last one,
so we're done with
the evacuation.
[VOLUNTEER SOLDIER 11A]
It sure took a while.
Maybe we should
getting back to-- Huh?
[VOLUNTEER SOLDIERS gasp]
[NAOFUMI]
Go!
Yeah!
What the...?
They took down a lizardman
like it was nothing!
There're still plenty of them.
Keep your eyes peeled.
[VOLUNTEER SOLDIERS]
Got it.
Ha-cha!
How did she do that?!
Thank you very much for your
help in the past, Shield Hero.
I'm indebted to you.
Where do you know her from?
You're that same lady?
Yes indeed. Thanks to you,
I feel much better now.
[OLD WOMAN 6A]
As you can see.
Wow!
[OLD WOMAN 6A] Small fry like
these are no match for me.
I swear by these arms,
which fought many
a formidable foe
back when I was an adventurer.
[OLD WOMAN 6A laughs]
[NAOFUMI]
What the hell did I give her?!
[AKE]
Sir Hero!
Sir! All the villagers
have been moved to safety!
That's great.
Now keep the enemy out.
[NAOFUMI]
It's been three whole hours.
What are those guys doing?
Sir Hero. You really should go.
We need to put an end
to the Wave quickly.
It'll help all the
villagers as well.
I don't know...
Ha! You can leave
the village to lil' ol' me
and these whippersnappers.
I suppose you're right.
Just don't push
your luck, Grandma.
Raphtalia, Filo,
we're outta here.
--[RAPHTALIA] Right.
--[FILO] 'Kay!
Master Naofumi!
Huh?
[FILO]
What a big ship!
[ITSUKI]
Keep it up!
[NAOFUMI]
Where are the others?
[ITSUKI]
They're on the ship.
I told them that
attacking that figurehead
and spawning the Soul Eater
came first, but nope...
They won't listen to reason.
[ITSUKI gasps]
[yells]
[MOTOYASU panting]
What are you doing, Motoyasu?
We need to take
out the skeleton!
We're gonna have to
take out the kraken first
or the Soul Eater
won't spawn otherwise!
[MYNE]
What are you saying?
[REN'S COMPANION 11A]
You morons...
[NAOFUMI]
This is no time to be bickering!
Naofumi...
Why don't you go and
defend some village?
I agree! An incompetent hero
who can't fight should just--
You're the incompetent ones!
[MYNE gasps]
Stop wasting time.
If we don't put an end
to the Waves,
more monsters will come.
And I can't do my job! But you--
Instead of working together,
the three of you are
doing whatever you want!
If we lose, all the villagers
will die, and so will you!
Quit thinking this is some
sort of game, 'cause it's not!
[REN] Don't you think
I know that by now?!
That's why I'm
hitting the skeleton
to spawn the Soul Eater!
Hah!
You killed it earlier,
but nothing spawned.
We have to kill it
more than once
to make it work!
I don't believe this...
[REN]
What's that supposed to mean?!
[NAOFUMI]
It doesn't have any special
parameters or resistances.
But there has to
be a way to spawn
a Soul Eater other than
killing that thing.
[NAOFUMI gasps]
[NAOFUMI] Raphtalia!
Cast some light magic!
Light? I can try!
Do it!
A-All right...!
As source of thy power,
I order thee.
Decipher the laws of nature
and illuminate my surroundings.
Fast Light now!
Hurry, attack the
shadow at its feet!
[RAPHTALIA grunts]
[gasps]
[REN]
Hm?
[REN grunts]
[ALL gasp]
Oh, now what are we gonna do?
[ITSUKI]
Look!
Soul Eaters are
spawning everywhere--
they're all over the ship!
Thunderbolt Slash!
Thunder Arrow!
[MOTOYASU]
Lightning Spear!
It's stronger than I thought.
Are our attacks
even affecting it?
[NAOFUMI] We'll get nowhere
with lightning-element attacks.
Filo! Cast wind magic!
'Kay!
Fast Tornado!
Come on!
We've got to take it out
before it unleashes that thing!
Right with ya!
Raphtalia, Filo.
Get behind me, quick!
[REN, MOTOYASU scream]
--Filo!
--[FILO] 'Kay.
High Quick it is!
[FILO grunting]
♪ Can't touch me! ♪
[FILO yells]
[yells]
[FILO grunts]
[NAOFUMI] This strategy
will kill it eventually.
But still...
[NAOFUMI] If we take too long,
the village will be destroyed!
We're not hurting it at all!
Stop complaining.
Let's find its weakness.
Raphtalia...
What is it?
I'm going to use Rage Shield.
Forgive me.
[gasps]
[RAPHTALIA] Don't you
remember what I told you?
You can always count
on me to be your sword.
I will follow you through
fire and brimstone.
Never forget it.
Take care of Raphtalia
if anything goes wrong.
[FILO]
Mm-hm!
I'll be here.
By your side until the very end.
[NAOFUMI]
Come forth, Rage Shield!
[yells]
[ZOMBIE DRAGON]
You will pay...
[NAOFUMI gasps]
[ZOMBIE DRAGON]
You will pay!
[screams]
I don't get it...
[ZOMBIE DRAGON]
For humiliating me,
defeating me as a puny human...
[ZOMBIE DRAGON]
And for humiliating me
by taking my bones and
turning me into a tool...
Is that...
Is that the dragon zombie
I absorbed before?
[ZOMBIE DRAGON]
You will pay...
You will pay!
What does "Grow up" mean?
[NAOFUMI screams]
[NAOFUMI]
A seething rage...
It's not the flame from before.
It's his hatred!
[yells]
What the hell happened to him?
Hey, wait!
Filo's being affected
by the dragon zombie, too?
[FILO yells]
[yelling]
He's basically turned
into a wild beast
and that certainly
isn't how a hero
is supposed to fight.
[RAPHTALIA gasps]
What the hell are you people
standing around for?!
Miserable demi-human,
how dare you!
Master Naofumi's
fighting in our place,
doing what we lack
the courage to do!
Yes, it's true.
If only I weren't so useless...
If only I were stronger...
I wouldn't have to
put him through this!
[RAPHTALIA]
You all have the power,
so why don't you fight?
How can you call yourself
the world's heroes?!
[NAOFUMI yelling]
[gasps]
Crimson Sword!
[ITSUKI]
Thunder Shot!
Hey, Motoyasu...
Why should I have to
help that bastard?
It's not right!
[ITSUKI] I hear you, but we have
no other choice right now.
[MOTOYASU]
Damn it!
Sir Motoyasu?
You can't be serious--
you're not trying to
help the Shield?!
[REN] Then why don't
you kill that thing?
[NAOFUMI grunts]
[REN, MOTOYASU yell]
[yells]
How was that?
Got to admit, it was cool.
But you're not doing
too much damage to it.
[RAPHTALIA]
Master Naofumi...
[ZOMBIE DRAGON]
You will pay.
Shut up. Just shut up!
Come out, you coward!
[ZOMBIE DRAGON]
I will make you pay!
I'll always believe in you.
[gasps]
[NAOFUMI] Didn't I swear
to protect Raphtalia, Filo,
and all the villagers?!
Shield Prison!
[NAOFUMI]
Not so fast!
Time for Change Shield!
[NAOFUMI, ZOMBIE DRAGON]
Within this virgin of cold ore,
who shall swallow
even your screams
with her embrace,
suffer in anguish
as your entire body
is stabbed and skewered!
I cast the Iron Maiden!
Finally put an end to that...
[grunts]
I don't, um... Master,
what just happened?
[RAPHTALIA]
Master Naofumi! Filo!
Are you all right?
Why? Don't I look all right?
[ITSUKI]
I'll be damned.
So that's what the
Shield's capable of.
So basically, he cheated.
You can bet things'll
be different next time!
[FILO]
Hey...
Don't tell me
you're a sore loser?
Th-That's not it, Filo.
I'm, uh, just sayin'
I could easily
have one-shotted that thing
if I'd gotten serious,
you know what I mean?
It was a no brainer, really.
Really?
Um, oh, yeah, absolutely!
Motoyasu never lies.
[FILO]
Then why didn't you?
Did you feel that?
Another one?
I've definitely never seen
this in the game before.
[gasps]
[GLASS]
How very disappointing.
You actually have trouble
with weaklings like these?
Are you really the heroes
holding the world's
fate in their hands?
There's only one here worthy
of being called a hero.
And what is your name?
How 'bout you introduce yourself
before asking someone's name.
[GLASS]
Oh, pardon me.
Whatever happened to my manners?
I am called Glass, and that's
all you need to know for now.
Feel free to consider
me your enemy.
Enemy?
I'm Naofumi.
[GLASS]
Naofumi.
Well, well...
[GLASS]
Then may I suggest...
...that we begin...
...the only battle of this Wave
worthy of the name?