My name is L'Arc Berg.
You can just call
me L'Arc, though.
Oh, and this is Therese.
I'm Therese Alexanderite.
Nice to make it official.
So, um, is Therese from a
foreign country or something?
Because I couldn't
understand what she said.
[BOTH gasp]
We forgot.
I deeply apologize.
Do you understand me now?
I do!
[NAOFUMI]
Oh, yeah.
I forgot my shield
translates for me.
Let's try that again.
My name is Therese Alexanderite.
[RAPHTALIA]
I'm Raphtalia.
[FILO]
And you can call me Filo!
Nice to meetcha.
You?
I'm Naofumi. Naofumi Iwatani.
[THERESE, L'ARC gasp]
"Naofumi," huh?
[THERESE, L'ARC laugh]
Hey, kiddo, if you're
gonna use an alias,
I wouldn't recommend
the Shield Hero's name!
[NAOFUMI] It's not an alias,
I am the Shield Hero.
[L'ARC laughs]
You? You're the
Shield Hero, huh?
It's really not
that funny, L'Arc.
But I do agree with him.
Your alias is a little
too conspicuous.
[RAPHTALIA]
Huh? But it's...
Shield Hero's got a reputation.
He's one evil scumbag.
Scams, blackmail, kidnapping.
And he's got powerful friends
that'll execute whoever
he doesn't like.
A devil in human clothing.
Actually, that's really
not too far off the mark.
Master Naofumi!
Obviously, I haven't
known you long,
but I can already tell you are
nothing like that creep, kiddo.
--[NAOFUMI groans]
--[RAPHTALIA giggles]
[FILO giggles]
Well, If you're gonna
insist on it...
Nice to meetcha,
Mister Shield Kiddo.
So you're all going to Cal Mira?
Are you headed there
to level up, as we are?
[RAPHTALIA]
Yes.
[FILO]
You got it!
Well, ya wanna team up
while we're there, then?
Bigger party is gonna make
things more efficient.
Team up with you two?
[knocking]
[SAILOR 22A]
Excuse me!
[NAOFUMI]
Hm?
All four of us are
greeting them together?
That's right. The crew
is gonna be so excited
to have the legendary
heroes talk to them.
I know it's really gonna
mean a lot to everybody.
Right, whatever.
[NAOFUMI] At least
this'll give me a chance
to tell them that if you believe
in the systems others are using,
they'll unlock for you, too.
[MOTOYASU, REN, ITSUKI groaning]
Hey, wait, how are you still
walking around, Naofumi?
Must be that overpowered shield.
[NAOFUMI]
Serves you right
for taking up all
the private cabins.
Anyway, I figured something out.
Remember in our meeting
when you were telling me
all that stuff
about item refining?
Please stop talking.
I really don't wanna think
about anything right now.
But you gotta listen to me.
As long as you believe
a system exists--
[ITSUKI] Seriously, the sound of
your voice is making me sick!
Please stop...
You just have to believe
the system exi--
[MOTOYASU retching]
[FILO yells]
[MOTOYASU groans]
[FILO grunts]
[BOTH gasp, scream]
Hiya, Master!
We're having grilled fish
for dinner tonight!
Wait a sec, Filo can swim?
Really? That's the first thing
you have to say about this?
Those fish stink...
Hey, Shield Kiddo!
Huh? What's goin' on with them?
[NAOFUMI]
You need somethin'?
Actually, Therese has a request.
Raphtalia was telling me about
how exceptionally skilled
you are at jewel crafting.
Would you be able to
make an accessory for me?
Well now that's random.
I'll help, but I'll need you
to give me the materials.
[THERESE]
Of course.
You can use anything
in this bag.
And obviously, I'll pay
you for your time.
[NAOFUMI]
Hm.
Now that's a gem!
I can work with this!
[THERESE]
What do you say?
It might take a while,
'cause I can't work on it
while I'm grinding levels.
If that's okay, sure.
That would be wonderful!
You got what you
wanted, Therese.
Uh-huh!
[L'ARC] Shield Kiddo,
I'll be counting on ya.
Oh! Feels like the
sea's getting rougher.
Guess a storm's brewing.
[NAOFUMI]
You think so?
[L'ARC]
Yup.
The crew's saying we're
in for a hard night.
[ALL groaning]
[RAPHTALIA]
Wow, Cal Mira is beautiful!
It's hot! The sun is blazing!
Uh-huh! Like the storm
last night never happened!
[NAOFUMI]
Why isn't she seasick?
That ride was way bumpier
than the wagon's ever been.
--[MOTOYASU groaning]
--Huh?
[MOTOYASU] I-I swear, this
isn't what it looks like, Filo.
[NAOFUMI] Well, somebody
had a rough night.
[HABENBURG]
Welcome to Cal Mira.
Pleased to meet you.
I'm Habenburg,
and I am the caretaker
of our humble archipelago.
I'm here to escort you
heroes to the inn...
[REN] U-Ugh, I don't think
I've ever felt so sick...
Well, initially,
that was the plan,
but I suppose I'll
have to start by
escorting the Shield Hero
to the inn alone.
[NAOFUMI]
Cal Mira Archipelago.
A group of small islands
bunched together.
It's a popular tourist spot,
and the legend that the heroes
of the past trained here
probably has something
to do with that.
Smells like a bunch
of crap to me.
The activation seems to have
brought a lot of adventurers
here all at once,
so they've given us
some ground rules.
"You can only travel
between islands by boat.
Try to kill as many
monsters as possible
without barging into any
other adventurers' battles
or stealing the prey
from any of them."
Is this a guide
to MMO etiquette?
MMO?
Don't worry about it.
So this statue...
...apparently represents
the original inhabitants
who developed these islands.
[RAPHTALIA] And there's
supposed to be an epigraph
left by a Cardinal Hero.
Is it this thing?
[NAOFUMI]
Magical writing...
As source of thy power,
the Shield Hero orders thee.
Decipher the meaning
of this message
and energize the
target of my choice.
Casting Zweit Aura.
[FILO gasps]
Oh I feel... powerful.
[FILO]
Nailed it!
So a hero of the past
left this here, huh?
Well, I guess that means
the legend is true.
[L'ARC]
Hey! Shield Kiddo!
Filo sure did get some
good height on that one.
It helped us figure
out where you were.
[FILO giggles]
You know, you kinda
hurt my feelings
getting off the boat
without saying goodbye.
[NAOFUMI]
I didn't realize I needed to.
[L'ARC] Company can
make or break a trip.
Besides, you never answered us
when we asked if you
wanted to team up.
Obviously, we've
only just arrived,
so first of all we'll need
to get our bearings here,
but we could help
each other out.
[NAOFUMI] Seems like they
know their way around a fight.
I guess it can't hurt.
We'll give it a shot,
but I'll drop you in a
heartbeat if you hold us back.
[L'ARC laughs]
Right back at ya, kiddo.
We'll catch up with you later.
Take it easy till then.
I'm a little surprised.
[NAOFUMI]
Hm?
I was sure you'd think that
somebody like L'Arc was
too hard to deal with.
I wouldn't say that.
It's just that he throws
me off a little bit.
[RAPHTALIA, FILO giggle]
[NAOFUMI]
It's already after noon.
We don't have much time,
but let's go grind some levels.
--[FILO] Okay!
--[RAPHTALIA] Right!
[RAPHTALIA grunts]
[FILO grunts]
Even one-shotting trash mobs'll
give you that much experience?
And even better,
there's an infinite respawn.
They're so weak,
it's hard not to get
bored fighting them.
[NAOFUMI]
Hm?
Is everything all right?
[NAOFUMI] We stopped
gaining experience points.
[ALL gasp]
[ITSUKI]
So you're responsible.
Itsuki...
[MOTOYASU]
What happened to my EXP?
[MYNE, MOTOYASU groan]
[REN] Hey, what are
you guys doing here?
I can't farm any EXP like this.
Go somewhere else.
Oh, no. Why don't you go?
You're gonna have to
leave, too, Motoyasu.
You know that I was the
first one to find this spot.
[MOTOYASU]
No, I was!
--[REN] It was me.
--[ITSUKI] No, me!
--[MOTOYASU] I found it first!
--Well, this is a waste of time.
We're outta here.
[roars]
[NAOFUMI grunts]
You're going down!
[NAOFUMI] That's a lot,
even for a boss fight like that.
I like this island a lot better
'cause fighting stuff here
is so much more fun!
Master Naofumi.
I don't know how much longer
this sword will last.
[NAOFUMI]
When did that happen?
[RAPHTALIA]
Maybe our power levels
have outgrown our
weapons' durability.
[NAOFUMI]
Yeah, look at Filo's.
[FILO]
Hm?
We'll just have to
make sure to buy you two
some new weapons before
the next Wave hits.
Uh-huh.
C'mon, we've still
got plenty of time.
All right! Let's see if
we got any good drops.
Huh?
There we are.
Those should keep you goin'
for a little longer.
This is perfect, thank you!
Yeah, Master. Thanks a lot!
[RAPHTALIA]
It's starting to get dark.
Do you want to head back?
[NAOFUMI]
Nah, not just yet.
I had a feeling we'd get
some better drops
after nightfall.
Enemies are a lot
stronger, though.
But we're used to
fighting in the dark,
so we can handle whatever
we come up against.
--But, what really worries me...
--Huh?
Master Naofumi, you still
look awfully tired. Are you?
So it's obvious.
Since using Blood Sacrifice,
my body's still
feeling the curse.
Just a little.
It's nothing to worry about.
I'm not gonna push it.
And I can handle the
enemies on this island.
[rustling]
Huh?
[ALL gasp]
Oh, thank goodness,
we found ya, kiddo.
Why are you out here in
the middle of the night?
[THERESE] The ferryman
was starting to panic
since you were
staying out so late.
So you two decided
to come look for us?
C'mon, It's not like
adventurers dying on a quest
is anything new.
That doesn't mean we're
gonna ignore you,
'cause I'd never be
able to sleep at night
if my associates were to
turn up dead or missing.
[NAOFUMI]
"Associates"?
Well, yeah!
What would you call us?
You wouldn't say
we're not, would you?
[NAOFUMI]
Well...
We haven't even
been here a full day.
I understand wanting to
grind as fast as possible,
but let's call it a night.
She's right, Master Naofumi,
it is getting late.
Raphtalia?
All right then. Let's head back.
[L'ARC]
Very well. In that case...
D'ya care to join
me for a drink?
[NAOFUMI sighs]
[PATRONS chattering]
[L'ARC]
To our safe return! Cheers!
[laughs]
Hey barkeeper, gimme another!
[OWNER 23A]
Coming!
[PATRONS gasping]
[MYNE]
Oh! Sir Motoyasu!
[NAOFUMI] I didn't know
they made wine out of these.
They're so strong that you have
to dilute just one of 'em
in a cask of water to get
something drinkable.
Pretty tasty just
the way they are.
Saying you can hold your
liquor's an understatement.
[NAOFUMI]
Hm?
I never thought there'd be a day
when I could just relax
and have fun like this.
[THERESE]
I'm looking forward to this.
I am, too.
Oh, and Therese,
the accessory you
asked for, it's ready.
[THERESE gasps]
Thank you so much!
[NAOFUMI] I can't believe
you had a starfire.
Those things are rare.
It helped that I already had
an oracle crystal on hand
that I used as the base of
the whole thing... Huh?
[ALL gasp]
[THERESE]
It's beautiful.
Huh?
This jewel's filled
with so much joy.
I didn't know you were
such a master craftsman.
Uh, do you have to cry about it?
Don't you understand, L'Arc?
Looking at this masterpiece
is opening up a whole
new world to me!
Um, okay...
All right. I'm really glad to
hear that you're happy with it.
Oh, and I hate to mention
the money, but, uh...
[gasps]
[NAOFUMI]
Whoa... This is a lot...
Not enough, though, right?
I know this is worth
so much more than that.
Hey, L'Arc, give him all
the money that you have, too!
Wait, wha?
[THERESE]
Just do it already, okay?
[L'ARC]
Why?
You can just pay me
in installments.
Now let's go grind some levels.
[L'ARC] Your party is pretty
high-level. Not bad, kiddo.
Therese has reached
Level 52 herself,
and I'm up to 56.
[NAOFUMI] Already got
their class upgrades.
Not your everyday
adventurers, then.
How about we discuss
our strategy?
[rustling]
[ALL squawking]
We can do that and fight!
[NAOFUMI grunts]
The shield's your weapon?
Committed to that
"Sir Hero" act, huh?
Keep talkin'.
Raphtalia! Filo!
[NAOFUMI gasps]
[yells]
Oh, L'Arc.
He's certainly having fun.
Power of jewels far and wide,
I beseech thee to heed
my call and come to me.
My name is Therese Alexanderite.
I ask my friends to be the
force that destroys my targets!
Bejeweled Ruby Blaze!
I've never heard
a chant like that.
[NAOFUMI]
Raphtalia!
[gasps] On it!
I never dreamed it
would be so powerful.
The EXP curve slowed down a lot
as soon as we hit Level 70.
Okay. Let's go after
the big fella, then.
[ALL squawking]
The boss by itself
wouldn't be a big deal,
but all these tiny
guys'll be a pain.
Just leave the
little ones to me.
I'll gather 'em all up.
And then?
I'll take them out once
he's got their attention.
L'Arc, Filo, and Raphtalia
can attack the boss.
Sounds good to me.
Everyone ready?
Let's go!
Hate Reaction!
[NAOFUMI]
Therese!
[THERESE]
Power of jewels far and wide,
I beseech thee to heed
my call and come to me.
Bejeweled Ruby Blaze!
[NAOFUMI gasps]
--[RAPHTALIA gasps]
--Master, no!
Now just relax.
[NAOFUMI] The flames are all
around me, but I don't feel hot.
[NAOFUMI]
Not only am I not taking damage,
it feels like the weight of
the curse has been lifted.
[NAOFUMI]
Just the big one left!
All right!
We got this!
[FILO] Are you sure
you're okay, Master?
Yeah.
What a strange magic spell.
My clothes aren't even singed.
Very strange.
I've never even heard
that chant before.
Guess there's more than one kind
of magic in this world, huh?
Hey, you wanna
divvy up the drops?
Sure. We get anything good?
Well, there's some
kind of weird item.
[L'ARC]
"Weird"?
See for yourself.
[L'ARC]
The heck is that?
With your help,
we gained a lot of
levels in just one day.
And it was fun!
I couldn't agree
with you more, Filo.
[NAOFUMI] You wanna
team up again tomorrow?
[L'ARC gasps]
I think we'll go it
alone for now.
Okay...
We'll see ya around
though, Shield Kiddo.
Thanks for a great day.
Thank you, too. We worked
really well together.
See ya later!
[RAPHTALIA]
You asked them to stick around.
That's not like you.
I got rejected, though.
[NAOFUMI] Maybe I should
ask them to join my party
after we finish leveling up.
Since we worked so hard,
let's take the day off tomorrow.
Yeah!
Personally, I don't mind
one way or the other.
But you probably could use
a break, Master Naofumi.
[FILO]
Hey, Master!
[NAOFUMI]
Hm?
I found another island.
Big deal, there's a
whole bunch of 'em.
No, listen.
I found a special
island underwater,
and it looks like
it's glowing red.
A special island underwater?
That's not all!
And there was a big brick
building down there, too!
We have kinda hit a wall
with our leveling grind.
This could be a nice
change of pace for us.
[RAPHTALIA]
Excuse me, Master Naofumi?
So, uh, what do you think?
[NAOFUMI]
Dressed like that,
it won't matter much if a little
water leaks into the suit.
I think it's great!
[gasps]
[NAOFUMI]
All right, let's go!
Okay!
[NAOFUMI]
This is crazy.
Ten minutes underwater
and I can still breathe.
[NAOFUMI]
Building's in perfect condition.
There's gotta be a way
inside somewhere.
[NAOFUMI sighs]
It'll be impossible
to open this door underwater.
[NAOFUMI]
There's air inside?
[FILO]
It's too dark to see anything.
[NAOFUMI]
'Kay, Raphtalia?
[RAPHTALIA]
Sure.
Give me First Light.
[NAOFUMI gasps]
[NAOFUMI] No way!
That's a dragon hourglass!
It looks exactly like
the one they've got
inside the cathedral
back at the capital.
Is that bad?
Anywhere there's an hourglass
can be hit by a Wave.
[FILO, RAPHTALIA gasp]
If a Wave attacks this place,
the islanders will all die!
Stay calm.
We don't know that's
gonna happen for sure.
Okay...
[NAOFUMI]
Hm?
This says the next
Wave is coming...
...in just two days!