Now fire!
The lords of Melromarc
will finally pay attention.
As you wish.
[CAPTAIN 3A]
Hmph.
Your will shall be done.
[MYNE chuckles]
That's no ordinary
forest fire, is it?
Got that right.
I bet Myne's the one behind it.
I guess she thinks
she can smoke us out.
I can't believe she'd...
That fire's gonna make it's
way down the mountain fast.
Let's move.
[PEDDLER 14A]
Checkpoint's been closed,
and there's emergency security
forces all along the border.
Gonna be tough to cross over
to Siltvelt for a while,
that's for sure.
Seems to be the
Devil of the Shield
abducted the
little Princess Melty
and is holed up
somewhere around here.
This oughta be enough.
Sure, lemme get
your change. Huh? Sir?
Have you seen this
man anywhere around here?
Oh! Master's back!
[RAPHTALIA]
How'd it go, Master Naofumi?
We should probably give up
on going to Siltvelt,
for a while, anyway.
Which means that...
Sir Shield Hero,
you are hereby requested
to meet with
Her Majesty the Queen.
Is meeting with
the queen our only option,
just like the Shadow told us?
Naofumi, what do
you intend to do?
I guess we're off
to meet the queen.
Now or Never
Just fight it out
Night sky reflects in my eyes
Holdin' up my hand to the stars
All the time is nearing
future's bleeding
But I want to be
honest with myself
Come clean Follow the wind (ah?)
I'm gonna make a scene
Keep it real, make a mark (ah?)
on the masterpiece
Everybody betray me
Touch of your hand
brushed me softly
Everything betray me
Shake all you want
But this feeling won't die
Through hundreds of times
through millions of times
I'm adding up scars
never giving up my faith
It' s proof I'm alive now,
always be myself
I gotta make a change
(make a change yeah)
In this distorted world
I follow the footsteps
Holding back screaming
everything is silent
Through hundreds of times
through millions of times
I Find & Create myself
Now or Never
Just fight it out
There are so many
demi-humans in this region.
Sure are...
I wonder... Oh, right!
What is it, Melty?
Well, I know the nobleman
in charge of this region.
He's a good man.
He might just be
able to help us out.
A nobleman?
[MELTY] These days, humans
treat demi-humans like slaves,
but in the past,
some nobility encouraged
peaceful relations
between the races.
The leader of that group
was a wonderful man.
He was the lord of
the domain of Seyaette.
But after he died
in the first Wave,
all the nobles who
had sided with him
were banished
under Father's orders
to the most remote
regions of the kingdom.
What is the king's
problem with demi-humans?
Huh?
Raphtalia? What's wrong?
The village my family's from.
It was in the Seyaette district.
I heard that
after the first Wave
the Seyaette region
was badly hit by rioters.
I'm afraid it was.
[RAPHTALIA]
My village was attacked
by a mob of
Melromarc's soldiers
who were totally
out of control.
The more I hear
about these scum,
the more I'm disgusted.
[MELTY]
I'm so sorry.
But, Melty, it's not
like it was your fault.
[MELTY] As royalty,
there must have been something
we could have done.
But we did nothing to help.
Raphtalia, tell me
everything you remember
about those soldiers.
Huh?
Once things have
been cleared up,
I'll make sure they're
brought to justice.
Thank you.
Okay, so this nobleman that you
know lives around here, right?
[MELTY]
Yes.
The real question
is whether or not
we can actually trust this guy.
[VAN]
You are indeed correct.
[RAPHTALIA, FILO, MELTY]
Huh?
It's been too long,
hasn't it, Reichnott?
Princess Melty,
it's so good to see you again.
Very pleased to meet you.
You may call me Van Reichnott.
I am the reigning lord
of this region.
[NAOFUMI] Wait, this wimp is the
nobleman she was talking about?
But his stealth
is off the charts.
How the hell did he do that?
However, this is
no place for a chat.
Why don't you come over
to the house and we'll talk?
[VAN]
I see.
So you reached my domain after
escaping Melromarc's forces,
is that it?
[NAOFUMI]
Yeah.
The knights have informed
me that you were the one
who started the
wildfires in order
to cover your tracks,
Sir Shield Hero.
Would you consider that
account to be accurate?
That's a complete lie.
I can guarantee the other
princess is behind that.
[VAN]
I thought so.
In fact, when I ran into
your party in the woods,
I had been patrolling
the area out of concern
for Princess Melty.
You must be exhausted
from your travels.
You're more than welcome
to rest up here for a while,
if you wish.
[FILO]
Ooh! Wow!
May I eat now, Master?
Please, can I eat?
[NAOFUMI]
No, wait.
Huh?
Not till I'm convinced
we can trust this guy.
[VAN]
Mmm!
Absolutely exquisite!
Rest assured,
the food isn't poisoned.
Okay, everybody, time to eat!
[RAPHTALIA]
Filo!
Where're your manners?
Put that down!
'Kay...
Come on, Master Naofumi,
I'm sure it's safe to eat.
It's incredibly
rude to cast such doubts
on his gracious hospitality.
We're not gonna
be here that long.
We're leaving tomorrow
morning at dawn.
But why so soon?
[NAOFUMI]
The longer we stay,
the higher the odds of us
being sniffed out.
Well, yes, but I was, ehm...
I was hoping to be able
to rest a little more.
Princess Melty, if you'll
allow me to say so,
it appears you've grown.
[MELTY]
Huh?
In the past, you used to
affect a mature attitude
that went beyond your years...
However, since you've been
traveling with the Shield Hero,
I'd say it's helped you to grow,
and I mean that in a good way.
[NAOFUMI] I'm pretty sure
you mean it in a bad way.
What?! You keep quiet, you--!
[NAOFUMI]
Quit making such a racket,
we're trying to eat here.
[MELTY] Whose fault
do you think that is?!
[RAPHTALIA sighs]
Oh, wow!
This feels amazing!
So soft and bouncy!
You need to get some rest.
Why don't you sleep?
There's no way of knowing
when this place is
gonna be attacked.
I make it a point of not
sleeping at times like these.
Master Naofumi,
why don't I keep watch,
that way you can go ahead
and get some sleep?
All right.
[MELTY]
Wait a minute.
Why do you listen to what
Raphtalia says, but not to me?
[NAOFUMI]
Don't worry about it.
Hey, I know.
You and I can do some
exploring around this place.
Sure. Let's go.
[FILO] I wonder if they have
some yummy snacks anywhere...
Would it hurt if you
were a bit nicer to her?
It wouldn't cost
you anything, y'know.
Huh?
[FILO]
What's wrong, Mel?
I don't understand why,
but I think I've been acting
really spoiled since
meeting Naofumi.
Even my speech has
become more crude as well.
I feel like a different person,
and I'm not sure I like her.
Well, I, umm...
I'm sorry. You don't really
understand me, do you?
Well, not exactly,
but I still love you!
Huh?
I mean, you always look
so cheerful and everything
when you're talking to Master,
so I can tell you like him.
Oh, really?
I know, all you have to
do is get him to dote on you
just like he does us.
it's simple!
What...?! Wait, no!
[FILO]
Yep!
But that isn't...
I mean, I don't...
That's not really what
I'm looking for from him!
[AULTCRAY]
You still haven't found her?!
If anything happens to Melty,
I'll have every one of your
miserable heads on a pike!
[KNIGHTS]
Yes, sire!
Rest assured, Father.
I promise you I will find Melty
and bring her back home to us.
Do what you can.
This can't happen
to my family again.
How much do you intend
to make me suffer?
Accursed Shield!
[MELTY]
You're up?
[NAOFUMI]
Yeah.
I'll take over now.
[MELTY]
It's fine.
I'm really not
very sleepy, actually.
What's the matter?
[MELTY]
Naofumi, I...
What is it?
I was just thinking that,
as a crown princess,
should I really
keep running like this?
As a member of the royal family,
there's just so much
more I could be doing.
But I find I'm doing nothing
because I keep running.
[NAOFUMI] You know, your life
comes before anything else.
So you can worry about
your duties once you're safe
and out of danger.
[MELTY]
But I feel so pathetic.
Don't be so hard on yourself.
Get some rest now.
[MELTY]
Okay.
Don't worry.
I'm sure there are things that
only you can take care of.
[MELTY]
Thanks. Umm...
[NAOFUMI]
Hm?
It's nothing.
Not important.
Goodnight, Naofumi.
Yeah, g'night.
[RAPHTALIA whimpering]
No... Please...
No, please, stop...
[NAOFUMI]
Poor thing.
She's having that
same nightmare again?
[RAPHTALIA]
Rifana!
[NAOFUMI]
You okay?
[RAPHTALIA]
Y-Yes.
[NAOFUMI]
We've got bad news.
[RAPHTALIA]
Huh?
[gasps] Why is the
lord being taken away?
Sir Hero, you and your
party have to leave now!
What's going on?
[MAID 14A] A nobleman from
the next town over marched
right in here and
accused us of hiding you!
[BOTH gasp]
Go find that
Devil of the Shield!
The kitchen is the
only safe way out.
Where're Filo and Melty?
What do you have to report?
He's not anywhere around, sir.
This way, quickly.
[SOLDIER 14C]
Hey, you there!
What are you doing?
[MAID 14A]
I'm preparing lunch.
Well forget that!
C'mere!
[MELTY]
What do you think you're doing?
I am Melty Melromarc,
Second Princess of Melromarc.
Let her go right now!
I command you two
to stop this right away!
What should we do?
I'm not sure.
[IDOL] My, my,
if it isn't Princess Melty.
[gasps]
[MELTY]
Aren't you...?
[gasps]
[NAOFUMI]
Let's wait and see what happens.
I'm so glad to see
you're all right.
I rushed right over here because
I was worried for your safety.
Idol Rabier.
I heard rumors that in the
past you'd had disagreements
with my father.
True.
May I assume that these
soldiers are with you?
They are indeed.
[MELTY] Then have them withdraw
from these premises immediately.
Before I do
something like that,
tell me where the Devil
of the Shield is hiding.
All I can tell you is that
the Shield Hero is gone.
Really?
I encouraged him to escape.
There's no way your men
will ever catch him.
He's too far away.
That girl...
I intend to tell
my father everything.
And I will do
everything in my power
to clear the
Shield Hero's good name!
[MELTY] Now, you will take me to
the capital as soon as possible.
Oh, I understand perfectly.
I'll make arrangements for
your journey at my mansion.
You'll be more
comfortable there.
All right, take her.
[NAOFUMI]
Calm down.
Don't ruin what
Melty's trying to do.
Filo! You can come out now!
Filo, it's us!
[MAID 14A]
Filo! Where are you?
Oh, to hell with it.
Filo!
Get out here now!
This is an order!
[FILO]
Ow!
Ow! Why are you being
such a meanie, Master?!
It's your fault for
not coming when I call.
And do you mind telling me what
you were even doing up here?
[FILO] Mel wanted
to play hide and seek.
We weren't doing anything wrong.
She said it was really important
I should hide somewhere
I wouldn't be found and not
to come out, no matter what.
But then she never
actually came to find me.
Wait a sec.
Where's Mel?
[FILO]
I'm going to save her!
[RAPHTALIA]
Filo, no, wait!
We have to get going,
if we don't hurry up,
then she'll...
[NAOFUMI] Abandoning her
and running away is an option.
I admit that.
And yet, she never
stopped believing in me.
So now...
I refuse to betray her trust.
I made her a promise.
I guess you know that Idol scum.
He's the one
in your nightmares?
Yes.
You can stay
behind if you want.
You don't have to come.
No, I'm fine.
I'm not afraid anymore
now that I have my sword.
I'm ready to face my past.
I know whatcha mean.
[DEMI-HUMAN 14A]
Open the gate!
[FILO]
What's going on?
[RAPHTALIA]
Demi-humans who love their lord
must've come here for him.
[DEMI-HUMAN 14B]
Return Lord Van!
Well, that's convenient.
We'll sneak into the mansion
while they distract the guards.
Let's go.
--Right!
--'Kay!
[IDOL]
Ugh, look at those damned demis!
What are they doing out there?
Why are they protesting?
[IDOL] Just some annoying
flies buzzing around.
Nothing to worry about.
We'll get rid of them at once.
And since we're mentioning
annoyances, my dear.
I believe it's time to tell me
where the Devil
of the Shield is!
I've already told
you several times.
I do not know.
[MELTY gasps]
[MELTY]
Reichnott?!
[IDOL] Where is
the Devil of the Shield?
I have no idea who
you're speaking of.
I-- The only shield
I've ever heard of
is called the Shield Hero.
[thud]
As you can see, we're having
a bit of a difficult time
getting him to cooperate.
I would very much like to
avoid getting rough with you
if that's at all possible.
But as a humble
servant of God, my dear,
I have taken a sacred vow
to punish anyone who sides
with the Devil.
That is my holy duty,
dear princess.
[SOLDIER 14E]
Intruders!
Over there!
[NAOFUMI]
Filo, time to go wild.
We'll go rescue Melty while you
take care of those soldiers.
[FILO]
Mm!
[RAPHTALIA yells]
[SOLDIER 14I]
After them!
[FILO]
Mel!
[NAOFUMI]
Raphtalia, what's down there?
Our priority right now
is rescuing Melty.
--We can come back later.
--[RAPHTALIA] Okay.
[SOLDIER 14L]
I found them! Over there!
That is highly potent venom.
If you don't take the
antidote soon, you'll die.
But I'm willing to give
you a chance to live
if you answer one question.
Where is Melty?
Stay away!
I truly adore this part!
That valiant look in your eye!
I want to see it become despair,
and watch as your
face warps in agony.
Come on, let me have
a good look at you!
Now what the hell
is going on out there?!
Idol, sir!
The Devil of the Shield
has entered the mansion!
Huh?
He's done what?!
Mel, are you all right?!
I'm okay, Filo! Raphtalia!
Don't you dare!
Take one step and I'll have
the pleasure of making sure
the princess's head will
roll all the way home.
[NAOFUMI] Oh, so we just have
to stand still, is that it?
[NAOFUMI]
Air Strike Shield!
Naofumi!
Why did you come back?
[NAOFUMI] Because I've
never heard of a hero
who abandons a child
to save his own skin.
You realize that you've
wasted all my hard work.
[sighs]
[MELTY]
But...
Thank you.
You dare make a mockery of me?
Torture clearly isn't
enough for the likes of you!
Your insolence can only
be paid for with death!
Raphtalia!
[NAOFUMI]
Wait.
Huh?
You miserable, worthless demi!
[BOTH gasp]
I beg you... [whimpers]
No, please!
Spare my life,
I'll give you anything!
[RAPHTALIA] So many demi-humans
begged for their lives
just like that, but...
...it wasn't enough!