[gasps]
[NAOFUMI groans]
[NAOFUMI]
Hm?
Anybody care to tell me
what's goin' on here?
[ALL gasp]
Master Naofumi!
Yay! [giggles]
[MELTY]
Finally!
Why'd you have to sleep so long?
[NAOFUMI]
What happened?
After we defeated the Pope,
I must've lost consciousness...
So they brought me to the
royal family's private clinic
where I guess I've been
asleep for three days.
According to Raphtalia,
the queen did everything in
her power to save my life.
[NAOFUMI]
I'm stuck here for a month?
But my wounds are
completely gone,
thanks to that healing magic.
[RAPHTALIA]
The curse was powerful.
Time is the only treatment
for the damage it did to you.
[NAOFUMI]
The Wrath Shield...
Blood Sacrifice...
"Powerful" is right.
But my body gets destroyed
along with my target.
[NAOFUMI] It probably would've
hurt the rest of you, too,
if it weren't for Fitoria.
--[footsteps]
--[NAOFUMI] Hm?
We're here to change
your bandages, I daresay.
[ALL gasp]
"Daresay"?
Another medic did it
just a few minutes ago.
[NAOFUMI] These two aren't
medics. They're Shadows.
--[MELTY gasps]
--[FILO] Huh?
[MIRELIA] I rushed over as soon
as they told me you'd awakened.
[BOTH gasp]
[MIRELIA]
I'm relieved that your life is
no longer in danger.
It's Mother--uh, Your Majesty!
[MIRELIA] Allow me to
re-introduce myself.
You were a bit
indisposed last time.
I am Queen Mirelia Q. Melromarc.
You saved Master
Naofumi's life and...
...I don't know
how to thank you.
Well, I could hardly allow
him to die, now could I?
The Shield Hero's one of
the Four Cardinal Heroes.
He helps to keep the world safe
from the Waves of Catastrophe.
[NAOFUMI]
That's funny.
Because this country of yours
doesn't seem to
appreciate the Shield.
Ever since I got here, they've
blamed me for everything.
[RAPHTALIA]
Master Naofumi...
[MIRELIA]
I owe you an explanation.
I was far away from Melromarc
at an international forum
with the other world leaders
to determine how best to fight
against the upcoming Waves
when things took a turn.
At this forum, we decided
that the major nations
would each summon one hero.
Then all four of us would
be able to work together
to fight the Waves.
[gasps]
[MIRELIA] But by the time
we'd made that decision,
Melromarc's temporary leadership
had already summoned
all four Cardinal Heroes.
This made the other
nations furious,
which forced me to travel the
world to put out the fires.
You're saying that trash
king and bitchy princess
summoned us here
all on their own?
They weren't even
supposed to have
the power to make that decision.
I did my best to
keep them on a leash
by leaving a lord I trusted
in control of the kingdom
while I was away.
However...
He was tragically killed
during the first Wave
and Her Majesty hadn't
returned home yet.
He was the kind and
just lord of Seyaette
until that happened.
[RAPHTALIA gasps]
[NAOFUMI]
Seyaette?
That explains a lot.
Hey, Melty.
Huh?
[NAOFUMI] What's goin' on?
You're acting weird.
[MELTY gasps] U-Uh--Wh-What
are you talking about?
I'm in the presence
of Her Majesty!
[MIRELIA chuckles]
I'm happy to see you've
made some friends, Melty,
and that you can be
yourself around them.
I encourage you to stay
in the Shield Hero's
good graces, Melty.
[MELTY]
Mother!
[NAOFUMI]
So...
Why was the Shield
Hero the only one
who had to go through
all that crap?
Aultcray already
had his own reasons
for despising the Shield Hero.
The Three Heroes Church
took advantage of that
to manipulate him.
[NAOFUMI] So he hated a totally
different Shield Hero?
What the hell does any of
that have to do with me?
[MIRELIA]
And Malty made things worse
by trying to ensnare
you the way she did.
I'm guessing things would've
been a lot different
if I'd been summoned by one of
those other countries, huh?
[MIRELIA]
Yes. Siltvelt, for example,
is ruled by demi-humans.
The Shield Hero is worshipped
there, almost like a god.
[NAOFUMI chuckles] So maybe I
should head over to Siltvelt.
If you do decide to leave,
Melromarc has no
right to stop you.
But first...
I promise to clear your name
and end the humiliation
you've suffered.
You have been a pariah in
my kingdom for far too long.
And to reward you for
fighting against the Waves
and eliminating the treasonous
Three Heroes Church,
we'll honor you with
the greatest award
Melromarc has to offer,
along with a bonus
of 500 gold pieces.
[RAPHTALIA, MELTY gasp]
Master Naofumi!
[FILO]
Hmm. Will 500 gold pieces
buy lots of food for me to eat?
[MELTY]
It sure will!
[FILO giggles]
Hooray! I can't wait!
Lastly, there's something
I'd like to discuss with you
in private, if you don't mind.
[MELTY gasps]
Hey, Raphtalia? Filo?
How about we head back inside?
Oh, okay.
Good! 'Cause I'm hungry!
[MIRELIA]
Isn't it enough?
I just know there's a catch
you haven't told me about yet.
At this point,
without your help,
Melromarc has no hope of
surviving our uncertain future.
[NAOFUMI] You can't convince
me to stay in this country.
[gasps]
From now on, I'm going
wherever the Waves are,
so I can fight them off.
[NAOFUMI]
That's the best chance I've got
to earn myself a
ticket back home.
[MIRELIA]
I understand.
Forgive me for asking.
How's your recovery coming?
[NAOFUMI]
Hm?
Well, at the very least,
I'm back on my feet again.
Excellent.
Would you consider a visit
to the castle tomorrow
before you go?
What for?
[MIRELIA] It will give you the
opportunity to clear your name
before the public.
Besides, King Aultcray and
Princess Malty need to...
[MIRELIA]
Aside from myself,
you are the only one
who knows about this.
And regardless of
whether you choose
to work with our country or not,
that won't change
what's going to happen.
This is Melromarc's way of--
No, it's my way of making
things right again.
[NAOFUMI]
But you're talking about
your husband and daughter...
[MIRELIA]
There are consequences.
Their sins are grave enough
that not even the
queen can save them.
The people know an
important announcement
will be made tomorrow,
and they've been instructed
to gather outside the castle
if they wish to
hear it firsthand.
And I have to be honest,
your presence would be
useful, if not essential.
Of course, I understand it's
hardly adequate recompense
for the way you've
been treated, but please.
[FILO]
See?
That's fun!
Master taught me how to
do this. Isn't it great?
What was it the queen wanted
to talk to you about?
Nothing too important.
She asked me to come
to the castle tomorrow
so she can clear my name
in front of everyone.
[gasps] That's fantastic!
Uh, yeah...
Thank goodness!
This means that
everyone in Melromarc
will finally know the truth--
that you didn't
do anything wrong!
[FILO]
Huh?
[RAPHTALIA]
I'm so relieved!
[CITIZENS yelling]
[gasps]
[NAOFUMI]
Why are you giving me that look?
This is what you deserve!
You both deserve to die
for what you did to me!
[NAOFUMI gasps]
[NAOFUMI panting]
[RAPHTALIA]
Master Naofumi?
[gasps]
Why are you awake?
You all right?
Don't worry. I'll be fine.
Yeah, but...
[NAOFUMI]
We have an early start tomorrow.
You should get some rest.
[NAOFUMI]
They're scumbags.
Why should I care
what happens to them?
[CITIZENS chattering]
[MALD]
Hey, why aren't we allowed to
enter the castle today?
Only the Shield Hero
and his party can get in?
What's the deal?
[RISHIA]
P-Please, calm down, Sir Mald!
[MALD]
Shut your mouth!
[RISHIA screams]
That's a pretty big
crowd outside, huh?
Yeah.
Hey, where did Mel go?
I think she went off
with some of the knights
as soon as we got
inside the castle walls.
[NAOFUMI] I'm sure she's
with the queen by now.
Glad to see you up and about.
Guess that overpowered
move of yours
didn't take too much
out of you then.
Believe it or not, I'm still
a wreck on the inside.
You haven't seen Myne
around anywhere, have you?
She disappeared as soon
as the fight was over.
[REN] She must be busy with
her duties as a princess.
Maybe she's putting together
a surprise party for us
to celebrate defeating the Pope!
Yeah, that's gotta
be it! Good thinkin'!
[NAOFUMI sighs]
[MINISTER 21A]
Greetings, Cardinal Heroes.
Please, come inside.
[FILO giggles]
Four Cardinal Heroes together.
I thank you all for coming.
[MOTOYASU]
Hm? Myne's not here.
I don't see the king, either.
You can bring them in now.
[gasps] Myne!
[gasps] Sir Motoyasu! Help!
[REN]
They've got the king in chains.
What's going on?
[MIRELIA]
That should be obvious.
These two are criminals.
[ALL gasp]
[MELTY gasps]
Let's get started, shall we?
The trial of the foolish king
consort and the first princess!
[NOBLES, RAPHTALIA gasp]
[CITIZENS chattering]
[NOBLE 21A]
What's this?
The king and the
princess are on trial?
Well, things are sure getting
interesting, huh, kid?
[MYNE] Mama, please,
why are you being so cruel?!
What is this?
My queen, what cause have
you to do this to us?
This isn't like you! [gasps]
[MIRELIA] With the Four
Cardinal Heroes in attendance,
this trial seeks to
punish those responsible
for shaking the
country to its core.
As queen, I shall
serve as judge.
[AULTCRAY]
What?
Don't tell me the Devil of
the Shield has brainwashed you?!
[AULTCRAY groans]
The Shield Hero has no such
ability and you know it.
I can't believe I even
have to say that.
[MYNE]
What's that?
[MIRELIA]
To ensure a fair trial,
you will be given a
temporary slave crest.
Mama?! [gasps]
[NAOFUMI]
Slave crest?
How can you do that?
She's your own daughter!
[MIRELIA] Because my daughter
is a pathological liar.
I'm not!
You know that I'm a good
girl, an honest girl!
[MYNE gasps, whimpers]
Stop! Please! Mama!
[MYNE groans]
[screaming]
[MIRELIA] Let us officially
begin the trial now.
Be warned, your crimes
are clear for all to see.
You cannot worm your
way out of this.
You can't convict them of
anything without explanation!
Besides, what so-called crimes
are you claiming they committed?
[NAOFUMI sighs]
We have to start there?
Let us begin with recent events.
Using a fabricated holy weapon,
the Pope of the Three Heroes
Church tried to murder
the Cardinal Heroes and
frame the Shield Hero,
but he was killed
in the attempt.
We're rounding up the remnants
of the Church as we speak.
[MOTOYASU] What's that
have to do with anything?
[MIRELIA] Appallingly,
the king and the first princess
were colluding with
the Church all along.
No. That can't be...
[MIRELIA]
Any objections to this charge?
What reason would I have
to collude with the Three
Heroes Ch--[screams]
It's appalling to think
the first princess
would try to
overthrow the state.
[MYNE]
N-No, I wouldn't!
Forget about the Shield,
they tried to kill the
other three heroes, too!
They even came after
the royal family!
I swear I would never
involve myself
in such a terrible scheme!
[MOTOYASU]
There, you see?
Myne really didn't
do anything wrong!
[MIRELIA]
All right, then.
What about your plan
to assassinate Melty,
the heir to the throne,
and then frame the
Shield Hero for her murder?
[MYNE]
Wh--I didn't do anything li--
[groans]
--[NOBLES gasp]
--Oh, Sister...
No, Malty. Tell me you didn't!
It's not true, Papa!
I promise you.
I wouldn't--[screams]
[MIRELIA]
You conspired with the Church,
and attempted to use
them to kill Melty
so that you would become
heir to the throne yourself.
When that failed,
you falsely accused the
Shield Hero of abducting her,
and set fire to the forest
she'd escaped into.
Do you deny it?
[CAPTAIN 3A gasps]
[MYNE] Melty is my own sister.
Of course I deny it!
[MYNE screams]
--It's true.
--[MOTOYASU gasps]
It certainly looked like she was
trying to kill the
second princess.
Yeah. We were there.
We saw the whole thing.
She wouldn't...
--[MYNE panting]
--Malty...
--How could you do something--
[MIRELIA]
King Aultcray,
you conspired with
the Church, as well.
You worked with them to summon
all four of the Cardinal
Heroes while I was away.
I only did that because
we needed the heroes
in order to counter the
impending Waves of Catastrophe!
On their first night,
the Shield committed
an unspeakable sin
against our daughter!
[MOTOYASU] That's right!
Naofumi assaulted Myne!
[MIRELIA]
Why don't we ask her about that?
Malty, were you truly
assaulted by the Shield Hero?
Yes, I was!
The Devil of the Shield
nearly raped me. I barely--
[MYNE groans]
[screams]
[ALL gasp]
--[CITIZENS whispering]
--N-No way!
--That can't be right!
[MIRELIA]
Well then, Spear Hero,
why don't you form a slave
pact with Malty yourself?
[MOTOYASU grunts]
Fine!
I'll prove that
Myne is innocent!
[MYNE groans]
Okay, now, Myne.
That night, you were
assaulted by Naofumi,
but you escaped and
came to me for help.
Isn't that right?
Yes, that's right!
I was so scared,
and you were the only
person I could turn to--
[screams]
[gasps]
[CITIZEN 21A]
That was a lie, too?
We all should've known.
All to frame the Shield Hero?
[NAOFUMI] This unpleasant
farce dragged on for a while.
My name was being cleared in the
eyes of the public, and yet...
...strangely, it wasn't
making me feel any better.
Is it because I know
what comes next?
Am I... looking forward to it?
[MIRELIA]
Hopefully you understand now.
Despite their status as royalty,
they resorted to dirty tricks,
attempting to eliminate
those who opposed them.
Concerned only with obtaining
more power for themselves,
there was no consideration
for the nation they served.
I didn't... I swear...
I was just--[screams]
[AULTCRAY]
I admit my actions may have been
unbecoming of royalty.
[NOBLES gasp]
[AULTCRAY]
But I swear I did it all
for the sake of my beloved
country and my family!
That was the only reason
I was trying to
eliminate the Shield!
The Shield's the Devil!
It will surely bring
the calamity of the past
to my family all over again!
I simply cannot let
that happen! Never!
[NAOFUMI] He just threw
away his last chance.
Does he really hate the
Shield Hero that much?
[exhales] It's time
for my verdict.
I hereby find Aultcray Melromarc
XXXII and Malty Melromarc
guilty of high treason
and conspiracy
and strip them of their status.
I sentence them to death!
[gasps]
[NOBLES gasp, murmur]
No... No!
--[CITIZEN 21C] Death?
--[CITIZEN 21D] Seriously?
[MELTY]
Your Majesty, that's too much!
This seems excessive.
I know what they did was...
[CITIZEN 21F]
I almost feel bad for her!
[MIRELIA] Your job was
to protect our people,
but instead you wasted your
time with a power struggle.
Even after the Waves came,
you did nothing to
help your subjects.
Who knows how many people
were hurt or killed
because of what you've done.
That cannot be forgiven!
You saw it.
All that suffering and loss.
All the pain that could
have been avoided.
[MELTY gasps]
[MELTY]
Well...
The execution will
commence. Immediately.
Send these sinners
to their deaths
in front of all the people
they have wronged!
[CITIZENS cheering]
[FILO]
Is this a party?
[NAOFUMI]
It's just like my dream.
These two criminals
will now be beheaded!
Those who turn against
the country and its people
deserve death,
especially if they
happen to be royalty.
We will prove that
right here and now!
[CITIZENS cheer]
[HECKLER 21A]
Yeah! Get 'em!
[HECKLER 21B] My daughter
died because of you!
[HECKLER 21C] Give me back
my home and my family!
[MYNE whimpers]
No, no, no!
[NAOFUMI]
Is this right?
Is it?
--[MYNE] Help me!
--[gasps]
Please! Sir Motoyasu!
Sir Motoyasu!
[growls]
[MYNE]
...fumi, please...
[NAOFUMI gasps]
Naofumi, please! I beg you!
Help me! Naofumi!
--[CITIZENS cheering]
--Naofumi, please!
[NAOFUMI]
Hold on!
[BOTH gasp]
[CROWD murmuring]
[NAOFUMI]
I think the death penalty's
too good for these vermin.
Death is instant release.
Do we really wanna let them
off as easily as that?
Her slave crest didn't
react just now.
She's got such thick skin,
she dares to beg the guy she
was trying to kill for her life,
and actually mean it!
When you think about that,
I wonder if the guillotine
could even cut through!
[CITIZENS laughing]
Master Naofumi!
[exhales]
So I've got a better idea!
From now on, the king's
name is "Trash,"
and the first princess
will be called "Bitch"!
Wha--Trash?!
[gasps] My name's not "Bitch"!
It is now, and it will be
for the rest of your life.
If you don't like it,
you can go ahead and die now.
S'up to you!
By the way, Malty often uses
the alternate name Myne
when she's adventuring.
How about that?
Yeah... Guess Bitch needs
an adventurer name.
How 'bout "Whore"?
[CITIZENS laughing]
[MIRELIA]
The Shield Hero is the man
that's done the most to
put things right here,
and he is granting his
oppressors the greatest mercy.
Therefore, Aultcray will
henceforth be known as "Trash."
Malty will be called "Bitch."
And her adventuring
name will be "Whore."
Finally, the Three
Heroes Church,
which was the root cause for
all this, will be abolished.
Melromarc will now adopt
the Four Heroes Church
as its state religion.
Four Heroes Church?
Wow, a church that worships
all four heroes equally!
Sounds good to me!
She just started a religion
that nobody else will
see as an enemy.
Smart lady.
Possibly the shrewdest
politician in the world.
[MOTOYASU]
Hey, Naofumi!
So where are you going?
Yeah, the fun's just
getting started!
[MIRELIA] I take it you
haven't changed your mind
about not wanting to
work with our country?
I'd still like to hold
a ceremony before you go,
to grant you your decorations
and rewards for your deeds.
[REN, MOTOYASU, ITSUKI gasp]
[MIRELIA]
Please at least accept that--
[NAOFUMI] That crap wouldn't
do anything to make me happy.
But I will work with you.
Huh?
[NAOFUMI]
Not just with Melromarc, though.
With every nation in the world.
After all, we're the
Four Cardinal Heroes.
That's kind of our job.
[ALL gasp]
You mean...
[MIRELIA]
You're correct, of course.
But leaving it at that
would not be fair to you.
If there's anything
else you would like,
I would be more than happy
to arrange it for you.
I'll think about it.
Sounds like we're hittin'
the ceremony ourselves.
--Yeah.
--Right.
[CITIZENS cheering]
[MELTY]
Thank you for everything.
[FILO]
You should come with us, Mel.
Now, Filo, don't be so selfish.
[FILO]
Aww.
Oh, Raphtalia, thank you, too.
I promise to do
everything in my power
to make Melromarc a better
country for demi-humans.
Thank you.
I know you can do it.
I believe in you.
[NAOFUMI] Raphtalia, Filo! Move
it, or I'll leave you behind!
--I'm coming! Goodbye.
--[FILO] Coming!
See you soon, Mel!
[MELTY gasps]
Ohh, Naofumi's a jerk!
Why does he have to be
so cold all the time?
And where are his manners?
He should've thanked Mothe--
--[MIRELIA sighs]
--[MELTY gasps]
[gasps] Mother?
If he hadn't stepped in to stop
the execution when he did,
I was going to offer up
my own life as a sacrifice
and beg him to
spare both of theirs.
Huh?
I wonder if he knew all along
that I would never have been
able to go through with it.
[MELTY gasps]
Naofumi!
[RAPHTALIA]
Melty didn't say anything to you
before we left, Master Naofumi.
[NAOFUMI]
Maybe she didn't care.
No, it's because you left
before she had the
chance to say anything.
Whatever.
[RAPHTALIA sighs]
Huh?
There's our Savior!
Hey look, it's the Shield Hero!
Master Naofumi, look who it is!
Huh?
Honor guard for the Shield Hero!
All hands, salute!
How 'bout that.
[CITIZENS chattering]
Take care now!
[MAN 21A]
Sir Hero!
--[MELTY] Naofumi!
--[NAOFUMI gasps]
Naofumi! Thank you!
Thank you for
bringing me back home!
And thank you...
Thank you for saving
my father and sister!
Yeah, sure.
See you later.
[MELTY]
Mm-hmm!
[NAOFUMI] The first time I
passed through these gates,
all my money, respect,
and trust were gone.
I'd lost everything.
All because I'd become
the Shield Hero.
And even though I haven't
gotten it all back,
I don't think I want to.
Because this Shield has
given me a lot more.
So much more than I
could've ever dreamed.
[NAOFUMI] Wherever the Waves go,
that's where I'm going,
along with my friends.
Because that's my job.
[NAOFUMI]
I am the Shield Hero.