[PRIEST 18A]
This is it.
The time is upon us.
At long last, our deepest desire
shall finally be fulfilled.
Thank you so much
for the ride, Fitoria.
We appreciate it.
And thanks for the new
wagon you gave us, as well.
[RAPHTALIA] Yeah. Filo really
seems to enjoy pulling them.
[RAPHTALIA]
Hm?
Uh--huh?
No take-backs.
It's all mine, okay?
She gave it to all of us, Filo.
[RAPHTALIA, MELTY chuckle]
Hey, Fitoria.
Is there another hero close by?
[FITORIA]
Mm. Very close, in fact.
Great, thanks.
[FITORIA]
Shield Hero.
Please take good care of her.
[FITORIA] And don't forget--
you made me a promise.
[NAOFUMI]
I know. I'll do what I can.
Now or Never
Just fight it out
Night sky reflects in my eyes
Holdin' up my hand to the stars
All the time is nearing
future's bleeding
But I want to be
honest with myself
Come clean Follow the wind (ah?)
I'm gonna make a scene
Keep it real, make a mark (ah?)
on the masterpiece
Everybody betray me
Touch of your hand
brushed me softly
Everything betray me
Shake all you want
But this feeling won't die
Through hundreds of times
through millions of times
I'm adding up scars
never giving up my faith
It' s proof I'm alive now,
always be myself
I gotta make a change
(make a change yeah)
In this distorted world
I follow the footsteps
Holding back screaming
everything is silent
Through hundreds of times
through millions of times
I Find & Create myself
Now or Never
Just fight it out
[FILO humming]
[RAPHTALIA] If we could
just get past that wall,
we'd be on the other
side of the border.
[MELTY] Are there any other
routes we could take, Raphtalia?
[RAPHTALIA]
Hmm...
We could take a detour,
but if we do, it'll cost us
a few more days on the road.
Yes, but Fitoria said
there was another hero
not too far from
here, didn't she?
It might make sense for us
to take that detour anyway.
[RAPHTALIA]
Master Naofumi?
What do you think?
Did you ever really try to
make up with the other heroes?
If you don't tell them
they're wrong about you,
they'll take it as an
admission of your guilt.
Don't forget--
you made me a promise.
We'll head straight
to the checkpoint.
If it's Itsuki or Ren, we might
be able to persuade them.
Okay.
But what do we do if
that doesn't work?
[NAOFUMI] We'll just have
to force our way through.
[MELTY]
All right, then.
[NAOFUMI gasps]
What is it?
[NAOFUMI]
Well...
I figured you'd try to
stop me from doing anything
that'd make my reputation worse.
There are men out
there, like Idol,
who are willing to
summon monsters
just so they can
torment innocent people.
This isn't the time to be
worried about your reputation.
[NAOFUMI]
You make a good point.
Uh?
[NAOFUMI]
Get ready. We're leaving.
--[RAPHTALIA] All right!
--[FILO] Okie-dokie!
[gasps] I-Is that...?
[horn blows]
Hey, Master, look!
It's that spear guy again.
It just had to be the guy
that was least likely
to listen to me, huh?
What do we do now?
[NAOFUMI]
It's too late to turn back.
We have to keep going.
[NAOFUMI]
Motoyasu. I wanna talk.
We're not here to
start a fight with you.
All we're asking is
that you let us through.
"Let you through,"
huh? Is that all?
[NAOFUMI]
Huh?
Is that all you have
to say for yourself?!
Traitor!
Devil of the Shield!
[NAOFUMI grunts]
Master Naofumi!
Can't you at least listen to me
before you try to
take my head off?
I won't listen to
anyone who uses
a brainwashing shield to
enslave Filo and Raphtalia.
You're despicable!
They aren't brainwashed!
[MOTOYASU] Don't even try to
talk your way out of this!
[groans]
[FITORIA] The Cardinal Heroes
are supposed to work together.
[groans] Dammit, Motoyasu,
just hear me out!
I don't want to fight you!
Hell, last time
I didn't want to--
I finally know the reason
I was summoned here.
I think I might be here
specifically to stop you!
[gasps]
[MOTOYASU]
Meteor Thrust!
[NAOFUMI grunts]
[NAOFUMI grunting]
[ALL grunting]
[NAOFUMI panting]
You're still not down yet?
You sure are stubborn.
I'll give you that.
Come on, Master,
let me at him! [growls]
If that's his attitude,
nothing you say is going
to get through to him!
[NAOFUMI]
She's right.
Why is he doing this?
Hey, Motoyasu.
Why exactly are you
so mad at me?
Is it because I ran away
last time we fought?
[MOTOYASU]
Are you that heartless?
Were Ren and Itsuki
that insignificant to you?!
People call you the devil.
Now I finally understand!
Huh?
[MOTOYASU]
You told us the heroes should be
on the same team.
You tricked us!
We trusted you...
You bastard!
I'm gonna make you pay!
[NAOFUMI grunts]
You're done!
I'll make sure of it!
[NAOFUMI grunts]
Hey! I don't even know
what it is you think I did!
Well, you should.
Think about it!
[NAOFUMI] He's seriously
trying to kill me!
--[NAOFUMI grunts]
--[MOTOYASU growls]
You're gonna pay.
You're gonna pay for
what you did to them!
Murderer!
[NAOFUMI gasps]
[NAOFUMI]
Murderer?
What do mean? Who's dead?!
Don't play dumb with me.
You know what you did!
[grunts]
How can you stand
there and pretend
you don't understand
why I'm so angry?
You might as well admit it.
You killed them!
And yet... here you are.
The heroes of the Bow
and Sword were killed?
How could this have happened?
Both of them were so strong!
[gasps]
You used your brainwashing
shield on Princess Melty?
You'll do anything, won't you?!
I'm not brainwashing anyone!
[NAOFUMI] If what Motoyasu's
saying is true...
You need to understand that
if even one Cardinal
Hero is missing,
fighting off a Wave
becomes almost impossible.
Now I really need you
to listen to me.
I didn't kill Ren or Itsuki!
Why would I wanna do that?
What do you mean?
[NAOFUMI]
Tell me this--
did you see their bodies
with your own eyes?
[MOTOYASU grunts]
I'll take that as a no.
So maybe somebody's lying--
[MYNE] I think a
representative of the Church
is a reliable source.
They said the
Devil of the Shield
unleashed a monster sealed
in the center of town.
Then you used the devastation
as a distraction
to kill Itsuki and Ren.
--[NAOFUMI groans]
--Ridiculous!
Sir Motoyasu, beware of
his brainwashing shield.
You can't let the devil
sway you with his words.
No need to worry about that.
He can't fool me!
I don't understand why
she's always like this.
What do you think?
Oh, no, Sister... You didn't...
[NAOFUMI gasps] You're the one
who killed them, aren't you?!
Enough chitchat.
It's time to battle!
[RAPHTALIA]
What is this?
You're using a Lightning Cage?!
An impenetrable prison
made of lightning,
sealing in the caster
and her target
until one of them can
subdue the other.
You won't get away this time!
I swear that I will
avenge their deaths!
Take it easy and think
this through, all right?
Are you going to believe
everything they say
without confirming it?
There's no need.
My friends are
trustworthy enough
to take them at their word!
[NAOFUMI]
This guy's an idiot.
She's got him dancing
in the palm of her hand!
--[MOTOYASU] You're finished!
--[NAOFUMI gasps]
[MOTOYASU yells]
[groans, grunts]
[MOTOYASU groans]
Shield Prison!
[NAOFUMI gasps] His level's
much higher than mine!
Filo, go!
[FILO]
All right!
[MYNE]
Oh, no, you don't.
As source of thy power and as
the next queen, I order thee.
How pretentious can
an incantation get?
Decipher the laws of creation
and bring down a rain of fire
that will consume
all of my targets!
Zweit Fire Squall!
I order thee to nullify
the rain of fire
and keep my targets
safe from its flames!
Anti-Zweit Fire Squall!
[MELTY]
Naofumi!
Okay, Filo, you ready?
You bet!
[FILO grunts]
[FILO yells]
[MOTOYASU groans]
Not so fast!
Zweit Air Shot!
[FILO gasps]
[MOTOYASU grunts]
[FILO grunts, yells]
--[FILO grunts]
--[MOTOYASU groans]
[MOTOYASU gasps]
--[FILO yells]
--[MOTOYASU groans]
Amazing!
That's the move she learned
during her duel with Fitoria.
She's making good use of it!
Forgive me for this, Filo,
but I must fight for Ren and
Itsuki, no matter the cost,
even if it means
I have to hurt you.
[MOTOYASU yells]
[MOTOYASU]
Meteor Thrust!
I'm not done!
Chaos Spear!
[NAOFUMI grunts]
Myne! Now's our chance!
Zweit Fire!
[ADVENTURER 18A, 18B]
Zweit Air Shot!
Behold the power
of a combo skill
with fire, wind, and my spear!
[gasps]
[MOTOYASU]
Air-Burst Flare Lance!
[NAOFUMI groaning]
Master Naofumi!
Zweit Air Shot!
Zweit Aqua Shot!
[ADVENTURER 18A yelps]
Melty.
Are you all right?
[NAOFUMI]
Hold on...
That's a combo skill?
Huh?
We can do what they just did!
You ready?
Okay.
[MOTOYASU]
Raphtalia!
--[RAPHTALIA] Hm?
--[NAOFUMI gasps]
[MOTOYASU] If you continue
to take his side,
I can't show you any mercy.
As source of thy power,
I order thee.
Decipher the laws of
nature and hide my target.
First Hiding!
[NAOFUMI]
Hiding Shield!
--[gasps]
--[NAOFUMI] Change Shield!
[MOTOYASU yells]
[MOTOYASU groans]
Sir Motoyasu!
[MOTOYASU groaning]
[MOTOYASU] He just stole
my skill points from me!
You really think that's
gonna help you beat me?
[NAOFUMI grunts]
I don't need to use any skills!
[NAOFUMI]
Filo!
High Quick!
[MOTOYASU yells]
Oh, no, Sir Motoyasu!
[RAPHTALIA]
Wide open.
[gasps]
[grunts]
[MYNE gasps]
[RAPHTALIA] You won't get
in Master Naofumi's way!
[MYNE groans] You dare to
strike me, you damn demi-human?
I'll get you!
How can you force poor Raphtalia
and sweet little Filo
to fight for you?
[NAOFUMI]
Still don't get it, do you?
Get what?
Filo! Melty!
As source of thy power,
we order thee!
Decipher the laws of nature
and bring forth a raging wind!
Bring forth torrential rain--
a downpour like no other!
[MELTY, FILO] Create a storm
to blow our targets away!
Typhoon!
[MOTOYASU yells]
[MYNE, ADVENTURERS yell]
--[FILO giggles]
--Nice work, Filo!
We make a great team!
We do!
[ALL groan]
Damn...
You haven't upgraded your class.
How can you possibly
be this strong?
Does the brainwashing shield
make you more powerful, too?
[NAOFUMI] While you and
your party have been
having fun playing superheroes,
we've been out here
doing the grunt work
to clean up after you
and acquire new skills.
Liar!
Do you honestly expect me to
believe it's as simple as that?
[NAOFUMI] Believe it
or not, it's the truth.
[NAOFUMI]
We do what we have to do,
no matter how
trivial it may seem.
That's why you lost to us.
I... [groans]
[NAOFUMI]
Give it a rest, Motoyasu.
It's your turn to listen to me!
Doesn't matter...
It doesn't matter
what you have to say.
I've got to avenge
Itsuki and Ren.
If I give up,
Raphtalia, Princess Melty,
and Filo will never be free!
They'll always be the Devil
of the Shield's prisoners!
And I can never accept that!
Not as long as I live.
'Cause I'm the Spear Hero!
That's Sir Motoyasu.
Fight until the end!
Bring me the Devil
of the Shield's head
and free my dear sister,
Melty, from his clutches!
[MOTOYASU grunts]
[NAOFUMI] How am I
ever gonna get through
to this thickheaded moron when
he's got a damn hero complex?
[FILO gasps]
What is it, Filo?
[RAPHTALIA gasps]
Something's off...
Look--all the soldiers
have left their posts.
[FILO gasps]
[ADVENTURER 18B yelps]
[ADVENTURER 18A gasps]
[MYNE yelps]
[ADVENTURERS, MOTOYASU, MYNE
groan]
What was that all about, Filo?
Master! Bring out the
dark shield, quick!
And a bunch of
other shields, too!
If you don't, then all
of us are done for!
There's no time to waste!
What are you talking about?
Hurry up! Do it! Now!
[BOTH]
Mm.
Shield Prison!
[FILO]
We need more!
Up above!
Air Strike Shield!
Second Shield!
What in the world is
going on here anyway?
Shut your mouth for once!
[FILO]
Here it comes!
[ALL scream]
[NAOFUMI yelling]
[NAOFUMI groans, pants]
[RAPHTALIA gasps]
Are you all right?
Filo and Melty?
We're fine!
[MOTOYASU]
What was that?
Myne, do you know
what just happened?
That power couldn't
possibly have come from...
It can't be... [gasps]
[clapping]
[POPE]
Truly remarkable.
You just took Judgment head-on--
an exceedingly
powerful group ritual--
and yet you're still standing.
[NAOFUMI gasps]
[POPE] I'd expect nothing
less from the Shield Hero.
[MELTY]
It's the Pope?!
I know you.
From the cathedral
in the capital!
Oh, so you remember
who I am, do you?
Then surely you're aware
of all your sins, as well.
My sins?
God bestowed holy
water upon you,
and yet you refused
to show Him gratitude
for that most righteous gift.
You also deceived the people
and led them to turn
against their own country.
You must be punished.
I shall purify you
in the name of God.
Your transgressions will
plague this land no more.
[MYNE]
How dare you, Pope Balmus?
Do you realize what
you've just done?!
You very nearly killed the
next queen with that attack,
and the Spear Hero, as well!
The Spear Hero and his party,
including the princess,
were murdered by the
Devil of the Shield.
At least that's the story
the world will be told.
As far as God is concerned,
you're all dead already.
What is this?
Myne, can you explain what
the hell he's talking about?
And if the lives of those who
have been marked for death
do finally come to an end,
that means all is
right with the world.
Everything shall be exactly
as God desires it to be.
This man's completely insane!
That logic's pretty twisted.
Reminds me of someone.
[POPE]
Oh, but don't worry.
We have a plan for
a new government
to take the royal
family's place.
What are you--?!
That's ridiculous!
This country's always
been ruled by royalty.
Our family are the
only ones fit to--
[POPE] Abuse your power
and disrespect the Church?
Look down upon the
apostles of God Himself?
Not anymore.
This country doesn't
need such blasphemy.
[POPE]
Royalty?
You're a pestilence.
And the same applies
to you heroes.
We worship those
who save the world
and its people from the Waves,
but this bunch has done
more harm than good.
For example...
The Spear Hero released a
sealed monster upon the world,
the Sword Hero
caused an epidemic,
and the Bow Hero
ignored his duties,
choosing instead
to serve himself.
Heroes that bring such
devastation to the country
and damage the people's beliefs
are truly nothing
more than imposters.
But... I, uh...
I only did that 'cause
I wanted to help!
Ren and Itsuki were
trying to help, too!
And you think they
were just imposters?!
Your arrogance and
foolishness speak volumes.
Just as theirs did,
when they decided to
investigate matters far
beyond their station.
[NAOFUMI]
Investigating?
Therefore, they forced God's
Judgment to fall upon them.
What are you talking about?
Uh--hey, wait a second!
It wasn't Naofumi?!
[POPE laughs]
This farce has been
entertaining, but that's enough.
[MELTY gasps]
The false Spear Hero and
the Devil of the Shield,
who clings so desperately to
life as if he were a cockroach,
shall be purified
with Holy Judgment.
And this country
shall finally be given
righteous order!
Be careful, Naofumi!
That sword's bad news!