[clinking]
--[FILO groans]
--[gasps]
What's wrong, Master?
Can't you get to sleep tonight?
[NAOFUMI] I just came
to check on the two of you.
Go back to sleep.
M'kay...
Good night, Master.
Thank you for checking up on us.
See you tomorrow...
Yeah. Goodnight.
In this empty void I
found the way to the light
Can't find my way
in this lingering world
Searching for the answer
the one that I can trust in
I'm just wandering around
Yeah, still stuck
in the shadow, ay
But I never follow that
This pain at last
Soon will pass
Turn into my own
unbeatable strength
This guy or that guy
dead or alive
by hiding alone we can't survive
I don't want to lie to myself
Keep on the fight, get right
I'll never lose and cry
Keep run up day and night
Time to rewrite
No matter what anyone say
I find my way, yeah
Never go away
Now, Nobody can stop me no way
I will make sure not to
forget those precious things
Yeah I'll take a stand
get back all that I've lost
Rise suddenly in this world
(I don't look back yeah)
This repetition will
repeat till the end
And the regrets are
still lingering in my head
Time to get it all back
now turn over
Rise suddenly in this world
(I don't look back yeah)
[ALL]
Hmm?
[MOTHER 8A] You folks would do
well to turn back while you can.
If you keep going forward
on this path, you'll die.
[RAPHTALIA]
Huh?
[NAOFUMI] We heard there's
a village down this path.
The village is devastated.
Even the village elder
got sick with the plague.
What's happening there?
We'll know soon.
[NAOFUMI]
Hmm?
[VILLAGER 8C]
Well, what brings you to
a godforsaken place like this?
[NAOFUMI]
I'm a traveling merchant.
I have medicines to sell.
Traveling merchant you say?
Wait, that filolial.
Could it be...?
Is that the Heavenly Fowl?!
Doctor, quick!
[HEALER 8A]
What is it? What's the matter?
[VILLAGER 8C]
Our Savior of the Heavenly Fowl
has come for us!
He's right there!
Huh?
[NAOFUMI]
"Doctor"?
[HEALER 8A]
I run the village clinic.
I-If I may ask, a-are you--
Are you really...?
[NAOFUMI]
I'm just here to sell medicine.
[HEALER 8A]
Even that would be a great help!
I can't make anywhere near
enough for everyone!
Good morning. Oh, Doctor,
are these people with you?
They just arrived.
They're going to sell
us some medicine.
[NAOFUMI] Looking at this,
I should probably
give it to them myself.
[FILO]
Here.
[sighs]
Huh?
[OLD WOMAN 8A sobs]
[NAOFUMI]
Fifty silvers, huh?
We can't thank you
enough, dear sir.
Well, actually,
it's a bit short.
But I guess I'll take it.
[HEALER 8A]
You were truly a great help.
Now we've staved off
the immediate crisis.
And that's enough for you?
All I did was
treat their symptoms.
I didn't cure them.
In no time, they'll be
right back to square one.
I'm afraid you are
indeed correct.
[NAOFUMI] Not that I mind, since
I'd make good money anyway.
Why don't we just
see which dies out first--
you or your pocketbook...
We know that we can't let
this go on... But there's...
There's nothing we can do.
[RAPHTALIA]
What do you mean?
We believe it's
the wind coming from
the mountain that's the cause
of the plague in our village.
The mountain that's
home to the monsters.
[NAOFUMI]
Home to what monsters?
[HEALER 8A] Around a
month ago, a large dragon
that nested there was
killed by the Sword Hero.
That, at least,
was the good news.
[NAOFUMI] Yeah, I did hear
some rumors a while back.
But wait a sec.
How does that connect with
the plague that's here?
[HEALER 8A] Many adventurers
came to our village,
mostly in order to see
the dragon's corpse,
as well as to purchase supplies.
That certainly did help the
village to flourish, of course.
But then, one day,
one of the adventurers
collapsed, and more followed.
The dragon's flesh
had begun to rot
and began emitting
some kind of poison.
[NAOFUMI]
Damn Ren!
Even a high schooler like you
oughta have brains enough
to know that meat rots
when you leave it out.
Actually, I guess it
must've slipped his mind,
since he thinks this
world's just a game.
If you know what the cause is,
how come you haven't
gotten rid of it already?
That mountain's filled
with violent monsters,
so the only ones who
even dare to go there are
the adventurers--there's
nothing we can do about it.
[HEALER 8A] And, perhaps
due to the dragon's poison,
the very ecology of the
mountain has changed, too.
Given the terrible consequences,
the average adventurer won't
go anywhere near the corpse.
Have you informed
the royal court yet?
[HEALER 8A]
Yes. We're supposed to receive
a delivery of medicine shortly.
[ASSISTANT 8A] But they
said that the heroes are
still too busy to help us yet,
so all we can do is wait.
They're too busy to help?
[NAOFUMI] Cancel the request.
Tell 'em you don't need it.
[gasps]
[NAOFUMI] Raphtalia...
Get ready, we're setting out.
Right!
Wait! You don't mean
to say you're planning
to go out there yourself!
It'll be far too dangerous!
Oh, you don't need
to worry about us.
We're used to danger.
I just can't find the words
to express our gratitude.
You can keep your thanks.
What I want is your money.
Five hundred silvers will do it.
[HEALER 8A]
Five hundred?! That's too much!
That includes hazard pay
so you can just give me
what you were going
to pay the court,
or were you hoping
for a discount?
"Savior," my foot.
He's just a lousy money-grubber.
[HEALER 8A]
You musn't speak like that.
I don't recall asking
anybody to call me a savior.
[RAPHTALIA] Master Naofumi,
you're deliberately trying
to make them
hate you, aren't you?
[RAPHTALIA] Anyway, I know we're
dealing with a dragon here,
but this is a lot more
than what we usually carry.
[NAOFUMI] We had to take
the wagon either way.
A little more luggage
isn't a problem.
[RAPHTALIA] We could've
traveled much lighter if Filo
hadn't thrown such a tantrum.
I've collected
a lifetime's worth
of memories with this wagon.
We can't leave it behind!
[NAOFUMI] Yeah, right,
a lifetime of a whole month.
[FILO growls]
[RAPHTALIA] I don't know what
to do about Filo's selfishness.
[NAOFUMI] You know,
it might've actually been
a pretty good idea after all.
[RAPHTALIA gasps]
[NAOFUMI]
We'll never get anywhere
if we try to fight them all.
As Shield Hero, source of
thy power, I order thee.
Decipher the laws of nature
and defend my target.
Fast Guard!
[FILO gasps]
[NAOFUMI]
Run right through 'em, Filo!
[FILO]
Okay!
[RAPHTALIA whimpers]
[NAOFUMI]
The air here is terrible.
Stay back if you're
having a hard time.
[RAPHTALIA]
No, don't worry. I'll be fine.
[NAOFUMI]
Okay.
But it would've been
a really good idea
to eat before coming here.
Looking at this isn't
doing wonders for my appetite.
[FILO chomping]
I don't know what it is,
but looking at it
sure made me hungry.
[RAPHTALIA]
Try not to overeat!
[NAOFUMI groans]
Given its size,
even taking it apart
will be a pain.
[squelching]
[NAOFUMI gasps]
[NAOFUMI]
It's a damn dragon zombie!
What the--?!
[RAPHTALIA]
What do we do, Master Naofumi?!
[NAOFUMI]
For now, just get away from it!
[FILO yells]
[NAOFUMI gasps]
A dragon?! I hate dragons!
[FILO grunts]
There might just
be a way to fight it.
Get behind me,
you two! And do it now!
[RAPHTALIA coughs]
[NAOFUMI] My shield can't
block all its poison breath.
I have resistance,
but Raphtalia doesn't!
But still...
If we don't stop it here,
it'll cause even more damage!
[NAOFUMI growls]
Now I'm mad!
[gasps] Filo!
Don't fight it alone!
If we don't get away
and regroup, we're finished!
We gotta go, Raphtalia.
Filo, c'mon!
[RAPHTALIA gasps]
[NAOFUMI]
That idiot! Hey! Filo!
Huh--?
Filo!
[roars]
[RAPHTALIA]
Filo!
[RAPHTALIA coughs]
[NAOFUMI growls]
[NAOFUMI]
Again?
Am I going to lose it all again?
Is this world going to...
take everything from me again?
[NAOFUMI]
Power?
Hate.
[NAOFUMI]
I hate it.
I hate it all.
[laughs]
[NAOFUMI]
Hate...
Hate!
How dare you
kill her! Filo! [gasps]
No! Master Naofumi!
[RAPHTALIA gasps]
Master Naofumi!
[RAPHTALIA]
No...
Not Master Naofumi, too...
[RAPHTALIA gasps]
[NAOFUMI growls]
[yells]
Master Naofumi!
[RAPHTALIA gasps]
Now burn.
[NAOFUMI]
Kill.
Kill them all.
[NAOFUMI]
Suffer.
Die!
[RAPHTALIA]
I believe you.
[NAOFUMI gasps]
[RAPHTALIA] I swear
to be your sword forever!
[NAOFUMI]
That voice...
What...
[RAPHTALIA] This is a world
where it's hard to find people
to trust, but I know
I can trust you.
I trust the great Shield Hero.
[gasps] What was I doing?
[RAPHTALIA]
Master Naofumi...
I'm so glad...
that you're back to--
[coughs]
[NAOFUMI gasps]
Raphtalia!
What is all this?
What the hell...
As Shield Hero, source of
thy power, I order thee.
Decipher the laws of nature
and heal my target.
Fast Heal!
[gasps] And heal my target!
Come on, I said heal, dammit!
Fast Heal! Fast Heal!
It's all my fault...
Stay away from her!
[NAOFUMI gasps]
C'mon!
[NAOFUMI] To defeat the dragon,
I have to use this power.
But...
If I lose focus,
hatred will consume my mind.
What can I do?!
[gasps]
What happened?
I don't--
Master Naofumi?
Raphtalia!
You okay?
Yes, I am...
Thanks to your healing,
Master Naofumi.
And... I'm glad we finally
defeated the dragon...
[FILO sighs]
Filo! You're alive!
Well, It took me
a little while, but I'm out!
[NAOFUMI]
You okay?
[FILO]
Mm-hmm!
But it ate you. And there
was blood everywhere...
Blood? Oh, that was
just the fruit
I threw up when
the dragon gobbled me up.
Seriously,
you threw up your snack?
That's so sweet of you, Master.
Thank you so much
for worrying about me.
Who was worried?
[FILO] Then why are you
looking away from me?
[NAOFUMI]
Get outta here...
[RAPHTALIA] So, wait, Filo--
you killed the dragon, too?
Sure! And you know what else?
While I was tearing at
its belly trying to get out,
I found a big purple crystal.
It was so shiny!
[NAOFUMI]
A crystal?
So that must have been
the source of its power.
And what did you do
with the crystal?
[belches]
[NAOFUMI]
You ate it?!
[RAPHTALIA laughs]
--[RAPHTALIA coughs]
--Uh-- Raphtalia!
[FILO]
Master, what's wrong?
Filo, we gotta
give her medicine.
Then we'll head back
to the village.
--[RAPHTALIA] No.
--[NAOFUMI gasps]
We have to get rid of
the dragon's body first.
[NAOFUMI]
You come first!
Stop worrying. I promise
I'll take the medicine
and then rest, and I just
know that I'll feel better.
Filo. Let's clean up this mess.
[FILO]
Mm!
[HEALER 8A] The mountain
wind has gone back to normal.
We'll be all right now.
Thank you so very much.
Go ahead and use that money
to treat Raphtalia.
I don't care how much
it costs. Just cure her.
[HEALER 8A]
Curing her will be difficult.
She's been afflicted
with a curse,
and a powerful one at that.
We've done what we can:
we wrapped her with bandages
soaked in holy water,
but we don't have a holy water
that's pure enough
to dispel curses like this.
However, if you go to
a church in a big town,
I know you'll find some.
Please keep this money
for when you do.
Thanks, Doc.
Raphtalia, how are you feeling?
[RAPHTALIA] Well, they've taken
good care of me. I feel better.
I never knew that corpses
could inflict such
powerful curses.
I just can't believe
how terrifying dragons are.
I know, right?
I shouldn't have been
so careless and gotten
all that rotten flesh on me.
[ASSISTANT 8A]
Hm?
[ASSISTANT 8A giggles]
He cares very much
about you, doesn't he?
Eh? Well, I don't think, uh--
Take care, Raphtalia. Bye!
[FILO]
Hm?
I'm really sorry.
Everything's all right.
It's just that,
I got this strange feeling
that power would take
you somewhere far away.
And I couldn't bear that.
And so, given that
I was able to stop you
before that, this doesn't
bother me in the slightest.
What does she mean, Master?
You're not leaving, are you?
[NAOFUMI]
I'm not going anywhere.
Oh! I have a gift for you,
Master! Right here!
[NAOFUMI]
Huh?
What's this?
It's a crystal I found
inside the dragon.
Filo, tell me you
didn't throw that up!
--[NAOFUMI gasps]
--Of course not!
I kept this one 'cause
I wanted to give you a gift!
[NAOFUMI]
If this is a crystallization of
the residual mana from
the dragon's corpse...
[NAOFUMI]
My level isn't high enough?
That shield wasn't
in the upgrade tree.
If I'd continued
to use its power,
I would've killed both
Raphtalia and Filo
while she was still
inside the dragon.
Master Naofumi?
[NAOFUMI]
Forgive me, both of you.
I put you in grave danger
because I hesitated
for an instant.
Just as bravery and
recklessness are different,
so are caution and cowardice.
If I remain a coward,
I'll fail to protect
the things I care about.
Back there,
I should've stepped up
and distracted the dragon.
There were so many
things I could've done!
It wasn't your fault,
Master Naofumi!
If only I'd been stronger,
I could have done more to help!
Yeah. Because I
hate dragons so much,
I charged in when
I shouldn't have.
You both are...
We are so much stronger now
than we ever were before.
And we'll be even
stronger tomorrow.
Let's keep that up,
one day at a time.
Yes. Together.
Yeah! The three of us!
Okay!
Wow, you smiled, Master!
Huh?
[RAPHTALIA]
She's right! It's true!
You finally showed us
an actual smile.
[NAOFUMI]
Did I? Uhh...
Yep! Right, Raphtalia?
He smiled!
Sure did!
[BOTH laugh]
It's getting pretty late now.
Time to rest up
and get some sleep.
'Kay! [giggles]
U-Um...
Master Naofumi,
would you be willing
to spend the night with me?
Feeling a little lonely tonight?
Oh, it's not that.
I just thought I should be
allowed to have this, for once.
--[NAOFUMI] Filo...
--[RAPHTALIA] Hm?
[NAOFUMI]
Sleep with Raphtalia tonight.
--Yes, sir!
--Huh?
[NAOFUMI]
You're cold, aren't you?
No, that's not what
I'm talking about.
What I meant was...
Aren't you going
to join us, Master?
It'll be more fun.
[NAOFUMI]
Not a chance.
--[FILO] Huh?
--[RAPHTALIA] Uhh?
I'm not exactly
a warm kinda guy.
[BOTH whine]
[NAOFUMI]
I have to grow stronger...
[NAOFUMI] Along with
the people who believe in me.
[NAOFUMI] And I'll protect them,
no matter what happens!