In this empty void I
found the way to the light
Can't find my way
in this lingering world
Searching for the answer
the one that I can trust in
I'm just wandering around
Yeah, still stuck
in the shadow, ay
But I never follow that
This pain at last
Soon will pass
Turn into my own
unbeatable strength
This guy or that guy
dead or alive
by hiding alone we can't survive
I don't want to lie to myself
Keep on the fight, get right
I'll never lose and cry
Keep run up day and night
Time to rewrite
No matter what anyone say
I find my way, yeah
Never go away
Now, Nobody can stop me no way
I will make sure not to
forget those precious things
Yeah I'll take a stand
get back all that I've lost
Rise suddenly in this world
(I don't look back yeah)
This repetition will
repeat till the end
And the regrets are
still lingering in my head
Time to get it all back
now turn over
Rise suddenly in this world
(I don't look back yeah)
I can't trust anything you say.
Eh?
[NAOFUMI]
Get lost.
[MELTY]
Please, wait!
You have to hear me out!
I don't "have to"
listen to a damn word
that comes out of any of
the filthy royal mouths.
Princess Melty,
His Royal Majesty calls.
Please come with us.
[MELTY]
Very well, I'll go.
I have to leave now, Filo.
--Mel, wait...
--Filo.
No. Don't.
[MIRELIA] Melty, I need you
to do something for me.
[MELTY]
Of course.
[MIRELIA] I want you to return
to the capital right away
and admonish the king
for his unjust
and outrageous treatment
of the Shield Hero.
Ordinarily, I would go myself,
but as you know...
You can always
count on me, Mother.
[RAPHTALIA]
Why couldn't you have given her
a chance to at least
explain herself?
Ya know, she's got a point, kid.
Hey, Master, I don't understand.
How could you
treat Mel so coldly?
Why? Tell me why! Please!
Listen to me, Filo.
It's not a good idea to
play with Melty anymore.
What?
Master Naofumi, speaking
to her like a father
isn't going to help Filo
understand things any better.
Why, Master? Why?
Mel hasn't done anything wrong!
Please tell me why I can't
play with her anymore!
Please, Master, tell me why!
Please, please! Tell me!
Master Naofumi...
Is this about Mel being
the daughter of the King?
[NAOFUMI]
I can't trust them. Any of them.
[gasps]
Excuse me, Master...
[NAOFUMI] Quit skulking around
and just come inside.
You have visitors.
I apologize.
It's you again?
What the hell do you want?
Uh... Well, uh, we...
Actually, I, uh...
Please let us
accompany you, Shield Hero!
At least during the Waves!
[ALL gasp]
[AKE] We were deeply
touched by your courage
and selflessness when you
fought in the last Wave.
Everyone here wants
nothing more than
to support you in
your tireless quest.
[NAOFUMI] Wait, is that
why you keep chasing me?
Yes!
We'd all decided that
we would ask to fight
side by side with you
the next time we saw you
here in the capital.
If this is about
fighting the Waves,
you can do that
without following me.
Just do it yourself.
[AKE]
No, Sir Shield Hero.
The point is we wanna
fight together with you!
You mind telling me why?
Because, Sir Hero,
we all hail from
the village of Lute.
Back then, you saved
all of our families
from a tragic end.
So you see, sir,
we wanna help in any way we can.
We wanna repay you for
saving our fellow villagers,
that's all.
[NAOFUMI]
Buy this for 150 silver pieces.
Huh?
[NAOFUMI] I'll consider
your offer if you can
cough up the cash.
Eh?
What's wrong?
You can gain my trust by
buying this trinket right now.
[RAPHTALIA]
Master Naofumi...
But 150 silver pieces?
Now what?
We'll just have to arrange it.
We understand.
We'll gather the
silver pieces right now.
[RAPHTALIA] I can't believe
you're pressuring them
to buy a leftover accessory
for that much money.
Well, I have to admit it--
you never change, kid.
Meanie!
[NAOFUMI]
Hmph.
[NAOFUMI] Fix these up
while you're at it.
[ERHARDT]
The made-to-order stuff, huh?
Even if I throw in some
freebie materials for ya,
it'll still cost this much.
[NAOFUMI]
Hey, boss.
Huh?
[NAOFUMI]
What do those stars next to Filo
and Raphtalia's
level indicators mean?
[ERHARDT] Oh, you guys are ready
for class upgrades already?
Class upgrades?
[ERHARDT] It lets you
increase your level cap.
Only those recognized
by the court
have the option,
but since you are a hero,
it's possible.
When you're
upgrading your class,
that's when you choose
which path you wanna take.
And I had a helluva lot of
trouble deciding on mine.
[NAOFUMI] You have to do it
at the dragon hourglass, huh?
What kind of upgrade were you
thinking about, Raphtalia?
I'm fine with whatever
you decide, I suppose. Why?
Oh, that won't cut it.
You've gotta decide your
future path by yourself.
[RAPHTALIA gasps]
After all the Waves are over,
I'll be going back to my home.
You need to pick something
that'll help you
survive on your own.
Huh?
Master Naofumi...
why are you going back home?
[NAOFUMI] We'll take
a skewer, pal. Thanks.
Right.
Can I really have one,
Master? I'm so glad!
[SHOPKEEPER 10A]
Here ya go, miss.
[FILO squeals]
This looks yummy!
[NAOFUMI]
Fifteen gold pieces?!
[SISTER 10A] Yes, sir,
a class upgrade will cost
15 gold pieces per person.
That's way too much.
[NAOFUMI] I could get
thousands of ten rolls
for that price!
[NAOFUMI] Okay, fine,
Raphtalia, you go ahead.
We'll upgrade you first.
--[RAPHTALIA gasps]
--[FILO] Huh? What about me?
[NAOFUMI] You can do it
next time we come.
Just be patient.
Fifteen gold pieces, right?
[SISTER 10B] Our apologies.
We have made a mistake.
I'm sorry, but we are forbidden
from providing upgrades
to the Shield Hero's team.
But... That's not
what she said...
It's a direct order
from His Majesty.
Tch.
Let's go.
Are you going to sell me?
Never. Don't worry about it.
[SLAVE TRADER]
Huh? Well, if it isn't Sir Hero
back with us again!
And how can I help you?
Looks like your
business is doing okay.
And it is all thanks to you,
if I may be so blunt.
Yes, your traveling trade
has been extremely
profitable for me
as well as you,
thank you so much.
What does that mean?
[SLAVE TRADER]
Your little filolial queen
has gained quite the reputation.
Nobles from every corner
of Melromarc are
contacting me to ask
how they can procure
one for themselves.
Quite extraordinary, actually.
--And then there's you...
--[gasps]
You've helped my business
gain a reputation for
providing high-quality slaves.
And the money just doesn't
stop rollin' in! [chuckles]
Anyway, how may I
help you today?
Would ya like another slave?
Or perhaps you need
some assistance
with your filolial experiment?
I'm trying to arrange some
class upgrades for us.
Can ya do that?
[SLAVE TRADER]
Ah... class upgrades...
[NAOFUMI] They're refusing to
let us do it in this country.
It's a real pain.
I remember you having a slave
that was over level 40.
[SLAVE TRADER] Er, though
it pains me to say it,
we don't provide
that service here.
[NAOFUMI]
I see.
No reason to despair, however.
You can still get it done
by simply applying
at any other country's
dragon hourglass.
You mean there are others?
[SLAVE TRADER]
Yes, indeed!
Ordinarily, I would charge
for valuable information
like this, but since
it's you who's asking,
I'll be happy to
tell ya for free.
If we're talking
favorable countries
for you to upgrade classes,
there's the Mercenary
Nation Zeltoble,
Demi-Human Country Siltvelt,
and Shieldfreeden.
I suggest Shieldfreeden.
Even though it's a
country of demi-humans,
it's surprisingly
welcoming to humans.
So how long is it going
to take to get there?
By ship, it's two weeks.
And if you go by wagon,
it's the better part of a month.
That's so far.
Yeah.
We won't be able to get there
before the next Wave.
[SLAVE TRADER]
Then how about making do
this time by equipping
your filolial queen
with a weapon? I may
have just the thing!
Huh? A weapon just for me?
[SLAVE TRADER] Wyvern talons.
Pretty slick, huh?
What's a wyvern?
How much are they?
In light of your
continued patronage,
I'll offer you the exceptional
once-in-a-lifetime price
of five gold pieces.
Make it four.
And how 'bout you
throw in some reins?
It's a deal!
You've grown into just the
kind of man I really adore!
You make my spine tingle!
[NAOFUMI]
What's with him?
These things feel kinda weird.
It might take a little while
to get used to them.
Oh, uh, listen.
Can we do some kind of
test on these new talons?
Well, I'm afraid
all the monsters here
are merchandise for sale.
Huh.
Come to think of it...
I may have just the thing
you're looking for!
Yucky!
I've never smelled
anything this bad.
That damned slave
merchant should be here.
What would monsters
be doing here
in the capital's
sewer system anyway?
They were probably
dumped in here
after they grew
too big for people
to control them anymore.
[gasps]
[NAOFUMI, RAPHTALIA gasp]
[FILO] Is that what we're
supposed to be fighting?
[NAOFUMI]
Yep, sure looks like it.
Raphtalia!
[yells]
[roars]
[FILO yells]
[grunts]
You're finished!
It's amazing how sharp this is!
These talons are awesome!
[NAOFUMI]
Hey...
--[FILO] Hm?
--[RAPHTALIA] Huh?
[FILO, RAPHTALIA chuckle]
[RAPHTALIA grunts]
[NAOFUMI]
Are you okay?
Yes.
It's actually not
so bad since the parts
you bandage heal really fast.
[NAOFUMI]
Ten days until the Wave...
I hope you've recovered by then.
[RAPHTALIA]
Mm-hm.
Since we don't know
when or where
the next Wave will
be coming from,
we're going to have
to be prepared
for anything and everything.
And given the
possibility of casualties
in a town or village,
we should stock up
on a ton of medicine.
Not to mention...
We should probably scout out
possible combat zones...
Uh?
Does it hurt?
Once all the Waves
have been repelled,
you'll probably go back--
back to your home world,
and I'll never see you again.
[gasps]
[RAPHTALIA]
May I...
May I go back with
you when you leave?
Master Naofumi, I hope that--
[FILO]
Hey!
How come you're being all
lovey-dovey with
Master? No fair!
I wasn't being
lovey-dovey with anyone!
You were! You were
trying to kiss him!
I was not!
You were, too!
I saw you doing it!
Ah! Will you shut up?!
Go to bed. We start
early tomorrow!
[RAPHTALIA grumbles]
[FILO]
Hmph.
[NAOFUMI sighs]
You've got it kinda rough, huh?
Yeah, it's okay.
[FILO]
What a sad-looking town.
Whoever's in charge
is a scumbag.
That toll told the whole story.
[RAPHTALIA]
If this town were to be attacked
in the next Wave...
Please, sir!
I'll give you this
for something to eat!
Actually, I'd much
prefer some money.
[VILLAGER 10A]
We don't have any.
We have nothing left at all.
[NAOFUMI]
I don't get it.
Aren't you people
from Melromarc?
No. We're refugees.
We fled out of the north.
Some say that an adventurer
was apparently sent from
this place to put together
a resistance force and
begin a revolution.
Now we're in this mess.
Do you have any idea what
this adventurer was like?
[VILLAGER 10A]
We don't really know,
but the rumors say
he used a bow.
--Bow?
--[BABY 10A cries]
What can we do?
Set up an emergency kitchen.
Right.
The Wave's gonna hit
27 hours from now.
Can we get something to eat?
Sure, let's go grab lunch.
Isn't that...?
Ren and Itsuki? Yeah.
I overthrew this
despot in the country
to the north, but y'know
what happened after that?
When I went to the guild
to pick up the reward,
they had already paid
it out to somebody else.
Same here.
I lost a job request from
some guy out of the blue.
[ITSUKI] Looks like
someone's going around
pretending to be us.
[NAOFUMI] ...she'll have
a kids' meal--large.
[ITSUKI'S COMRADE 10A]
Itsuki...
We've just received
another guild request
to overthrow a town
lord to the north.
What do you want
to do with this?
[ITSUKI]
From the guild?
Yes. From what I can tell,
it seems that the local lord
is heavily taxing the citizens,
way beyond the
court's set limits,
and he's using that revenue
in a vicious campaign
to suppress dissenters
of any kind
and to hire mercenaries.
[NAOFUMI] Are they're talking
about those townspeople
we just met?
[WAITER 10A]
Okay! Here's your food.
[FILO]
That looks yummy!
Time to dig in!
[RAPHTALIA]
Chew before you swallow, Filo.
Interesting...
They need to be taught that
with great power comes
great responsibility.
[yelps]
[FILO]
Master, that's gross!
Sorry, Filo. [chuckles]
[ITSUKI]
What's so funny?
Huh?
Hey, I had no idea you'd
been bitten by a spider, pal.
Bitten by a what?
Never mind.
Just forget I said it.
It's you, huh?!
You're the one who's
been impersonating us,
stealing our jobs and
taking our rewards.
[NAOFUMI] What the hell
would I do that for?
Who else would come up
with an idea like--
[NAOFUMI]
Did you ever think that may be
you're trying too hard
to be some sort of
supercool secret vigilante?
And that you're not
very good at it?
[ITSUKI]
What do you mean?
[NAOFUMI]
You were the "adventurer"
who helped the resistance
in the north, weren't you?
Yeah.
[NAOFUMI]
Do you have the slightest idea
what happened to that country
after the king was ousted?
Is this everyone
from your village?
Yes. Everybody else was killed.
After the revolution,
to be honest,
our lives did get a little
better. But not for long.
The resistance started
hiking up the taxes
just like the lord
had done before.
But why would they do that?
[VILLAGER 10A]
I don't know too much about it,
but apparently it takes
an awful lot of money
to run a country.
Now that I think of it,
maybe the previous king had
the exact same thing in mind.
[NAOFUMI]
And all you did was switch
who was running the village.
It never solved a damn thing.
Stop trying to
change the subject!
We're talking about
you impersonating my--
[REN]
How do you explain my case?
What was it about, some disease?
If you know,
that makes it easier.
So why'd you steal that job?
Did you know the
corpse of that dragon
you killed caused an epidemic
that nearly wiped out
the entire village?
[gasps]
[NAOFUMI]
I got rid of that corpse.
That's why the job
request was canceled.
No way...
It's true, and if
you think I'm lying,
go there and see for yourself.
Do you have any idea
how many people
died because of you two?!
[BOTH gasp]
[REN gasps]
Because of what I did?
Master Naofumi...
[REN]
I see. I'm sorry.
You mean you believe him?
Why shouldn't I?
He has no reason to lie.
[NAOFUMI]
Don't cause any more problems.
[ITSUKI]
I still don't believe you.
[ERHARDT] I embedded
that dragon zombie core
in your chest plate
and even gave it
an auto-repair function.
It's probably my best work.
What do ya say?
Ugh. Tell me honestly,
just how badly
do you wanna make me look
like the king of the bandits?
You look so cool--
really, Master!
I think it's very nice!
[AKE]
Pardon us.
Oh, thank goodness you're here!
I thought we'd missed you.
We ran around all over town
and somehow managed to scrape up
150 silver pieces for you.
[NAOFUMI]
Go on.
Use that money to get
yourselves better equipment.
Eh? You mean you'll accept us?
I can't have you guys
dropping like flies.
Thank you very much!
[NAOFUMI]
Don't get the wrong idea.
The second you try to
exploit me or set me up,
you'll regret it
for the rest of your lives.
Of course!
[GROUP]
Thanks for having us!
Master, now we have
so many more friends!
[NAOFUMI] There are less than
24 hours until the Wave.
Let's have a strategy meeting.
--[FILO] Okay!
--[GROUP] Right!
Oh, don't gimme that again!
My shop isn't exactly
your meeting room, y'know!
[BLACK-CLAD WOMAN 5A]
Melty appears to have made
contact with the Shield Hero's
party, Your Majesty.
[MIRELIA] If the Shield
Hero is the kind of man
I hear he is, reconciliation
will take quite some time.
I feel bad for putting
Melty through this,
but this, too, is her duty
as the future ruler.
Your Majesty?
[MIRELIA]
Continue to keep an eye on them.
[BLACK-CLAD WOMAN 5A]
As you wish.
[MIRELIA gasps]
The Wave is nearly here.
Will the heroes be
able to overcome it?