[chattering]
Thanks to our heroes,
the battle was splendidly won.
And tonight, we celebrate!
Enjoy yourselves to the fullest!
[GUESTS]
Hooray!
[NOBLEMAN 4A]
Weren't the heroes fantastic?
[NOBLEMAN 4B] Our country
has nothing to worry about.
[NAOFUMI]
This is ridiculous.
I wouldn't even be here
if it wasn't for the reward.
[NOBLEMAN 4C]
And the latest reports say
that there were very
few casualties.
We all owe everything
to our brave heroes.
Well I did my part.
I held my ground against
a massive monster
and fought with honor
as a royal knight!
Yeah...
[NOBLEWOMAN 4B] I'm so
truly honored to meet you,
brave Spear Hero.
[NOBLEWOMAN 4C] You don't
happen to have a lover, do you?
Oh, hey, uh...
SIr Motoyasu has
no time for that.
[MOTOYASU gasps]
[MOTOYASU]
Uh--hey, wait! You!
[MYNE]
Sir Motoyasu.
Uh?
[inaudible]
[RAPHTALIA]
Master Naofumi.
The food here
really looks amazing!
You sure you don't
want something to eat?
[NAOFUMI]
If you want to eat, go ahead.
I'd really like
for you to join me.
[NAOFUMI]
I'll pass.
[NAOFUMI] So I can
teleport people with me?
[NAOFUMI] That would've
come in real handy before.
You sure you don't
want some food?
How about you try a
little for me, huh?
Uh, no. I don't want it--
[RAPHTALIA]
It's really good, I promise.
Uh--
See?
[MOTOYASU]
Naofumi...
[NAOFUMI gasps]
Hmm?
[GUESTS gasp]
Time to fight.
[RAPHTALIA gasps]
In this empty void I
found the way to the light
Can't find my way
in this lingering world
Searching for the answer
the one that I can trust in
I'm just wandering around
Yeah, still stuck
in the shadow, ay
But I never follow that
This pain at last
Soon will pass
Turn into my own
unbeatable strength
This guy or that guy
dead or alive
by hiding alone we can't survive
I don't want to lie to myself
Keep on the fight, get right
I'll never lose and cry
Keep run up day and night
Time to rewrite
No matter what anyone say
I find my way, yeah
Never go away
Now, Nobody can stop me no way
I will make sure not to
forget those precious things
Yeah I'll take a stand
get back all that I've lost
Rise suddenly in this world
(I don't look back yeah)
This repetition will
repeat till the end
And the regrets are
still lingering in my head
Time to get it all back
now turn over
Rise suddenly in this world
(I don't look back yeah)
[GUESTS whispering]
[MOTOYASU]
I've heard that you've
made poor Raphtalia your slave
and that she obeys
your every command.
Huh?
And what do you care?
Watch your tone.
Yeah, Raphtalia's
my loyal slave.
So what's it to you?
You listen up.
You can't be saying you think
it's okay to enslave others!
D'you even hear yourself?
Slavery's legal
in this crazy place
and she's been a
great help to me.
But we're heroes in this world!
We shouldn't behave that
way here and you know it.
[NAOFUMI] You have a
right to your opinion.
And I disagree.
[MOTOYASU growls]
--[MOTOYASU] Let's do this!
--[RAPHTALIA gasps]
And if I win, you're
gonna set Raphtalia free.
All right. What's the plan
if I win this fight?
That won't happen.
But if it does,
things'll stay the same.
Don't be such an idiot.
Master Naofumi!
He actually has a
slave in his party?
Man, how much lower
is this guy gonna go?
[AULTCRAY] It has been
brought to my attention...
...that you, a hero, have been
using a demi-human as your slave
to fight for you.
You violated our customs
and that is reprehensible.
[MYNE chuckles]
I order you.
Accept the challenge!
[GUESTS gasp]
[gasps] Hey! They
don't need to fight!
I'm with Master Naofumi
of my own free will and--
You leave her alone!
Ah, you poor creature.
You've been placed under a curse
that forces you to defend him,
have you not?
[RAPHTALIA grunts, groans]
[AULTCRAY] Don't worry.
Once Master Motoyasu wins,
you shall be released
from that curse.
Stop it! C'mon, don't hurt her!
Draw swords!
--[NOBLEWOMEN gasp]
--[NAOFUMI grunts]
[AULTCRAY]
Heed my order,
or I shall take her
from you by force.
There is no way that you're
getting out of this, you coward.
You're a scumbag!
--[MOTOYASU gasps]
--I will win
and Raphtalia will
be returned to me!
[MYNE chuckles]
[MYNE] And how exactly will you
win without her, Shield Hero?
[GUESTS chuckling]
[MINISTER 4B]
The duel between the Spear Hero
and the Shield Hero
will now begin!
This duel will end only
when one of the combatants
is either pinned, or admits
that he has been defeated.
[gasps]
[MINISTER 4B] This duel will
take place in the presence of
King Melromarc and the Pope,
and it is thus
legitimate and official.
[SPECTATORS gasp]
[MYNE]
Sir Motoyasu! Best of luck!
[MOTOYASU]
Remember the folk tale about
the irresistible spear
and the immovable shield?
Naofumi, be a man
and admit defeat!
[MINISTER 4B]
Ready...
Begin!
[MOTOYASU yells]
[NAOFUMI grunting]
Not too bad!
I guess the Shield Hero
has a few moves.
[NAOFUMI]
You got that right.
[gasps]
So in this folk tale battle
between a spear and a shield,
did you know that the
spear actually lost
when it couldn't
pierce the shield?
[MOTOYASU grunts]
Chaos Spear!
[NAOFUMI grunts]
[groans, gasps]
[RAPHTALIA grunts]
[NAOFUMI pants]
[groans]
[NAOFUMI grunts]
[MOTOYASU yells]
[chuckles] He's trying to
strike using the shield?
That'll never--[gasps]
[groans] What--?
Get off!
A balloon? Used as
a battle weapon?
--[SPECTATORS gasp]
--[BALLOONS growling]
[NAOFUMI]
Heh.
Tell me, what the
hell are you up to?
If it's true that I can't win,
I'm gonna hurt you as
much as I possibly can.
Like hell!
[MOTOYASU] C'mon, Shield Hero!
You gotta fight fair!
[MOTOYASU gasps]
Get off of me!
Air Strike Shield!
[NAOFUMI]
Shield Prison!
[gasps]
[MOTOYASU]
Hey! Stop that! No!
Hey! That hurts!
[SPECTATOR 4A]
It can't be.
[SPECTATOR 4B] At this rate,
the Shield Hero might win.
Naofumi and his shield
have the upper hand.
[REN]
Hm.
Does that lowly Shield Hero
think he can win
against the Spear Hero?
Have you no respect for
the sanctity of a duel?!
[grunts]
[NAOFUMI] It's time for
you to admit defeat.
Or do you want more
embarrassment, tough guy?
[MOTOYASU exhales] And why
would I ever surrender now?
[NAOFUMI]
All right, I see.
So then. Guess I'll take
aim at your handsome face
and that precious
manhood of yours.
[gasps]
Might as well, since
I'm a cowardly cheater!
Ahh! No!
[NAOFUMI gasps, groans]
[NAOFUMI groans]
[NAOFUMI]
Magic? She has magic?
[yells]
[gasps]
[NAOFUMI grunting]
[MOTOYASU grunts]
Lightning Spear!
[NAOFUMI grunts, yells]
[NAOFUMI groans]
[RAPHTALIA grunts]
[MOTOYASU pants]
The battle... has been won.
[SPECTATORS cheering]
[AULTCRAY chuckles]
[NAOFUMI groans]
[NAOFUMI]
You didn't win.
[MOTOYASU]
Huh?
So what happened to this
being a one-on-one duel?
And it's obvious
that you didn't win.
What?
[NAOFUMI] That magician
butted in and gave you help!
Ha! Little man's a sore loser?
It's the truth!
Everyone who was watching
her could see it!
You all saw Myne use
her magic, didn't you?
I know you saw it!
She used her magic
to help him win!
There's no way.
They must have seen it.
I shall listen to no more
arguments about this battle.
Brave Spear Hero,
you have won the duel!
[MYNE giggles]
I knew you would win.
[sighs] Sir Motoyasu.
You knew, huh?
[sighs]
Too bad, Shield Hero. You must
be so upset about your loss.
It really is such a shame
that you'll have to go back
to fighting all by yourself.
--[MYNE laughing]
--[NAOFUMI growls]
Your fighting was brilliant,
Master Motoyasu.
[MOTOYASU]
Sir.
Now I know why
my daughter, Malty,
chooses to believe
so much in you.
[MYNE giggles]
You see, Papa?
[NAOFUMI gasps]
[MOTOYASU] I gotta say,
it was a total shock
to learn that Myne was
the King's daughter.
[MYNE]
I am.
But I fight to contribute
to the world's peace.
[NAOFUMI] So... this entire
thing... was planned!
The princess framed me
to get in the good graces
of her favorite hero.
And her father twisted the facts
to please his dear daughter.
Even this duel was
a setup all along!
I know that the Shield Hero
has forced that poor girl
to be his slave.
You must save her.
[MOTOYASU gasps]
[NAOFUMI]
I just don't understand...
...why they want to
see me fail like this.
[NAOFUMI] I didn't come to
this world because I wanted to.
You wanted it!
You summoned me here!
So why are they
doing this to me?
The girl who was enslaved
by the cowardly Shield Hero
has been given her freedom
by the triumphant Spear Hero!
[SPECTATORS gasp]
[NOBLEWOMAN 4E] It's clear
that we should never have
summoned the Shield
Hero to begin with!
The other three serve us well!
We should just get rid
of that criminal scum
as soon as possible.
[NOBLEMAN 4F] Our country
doesn't need the Shield!
[NOBLEMAN 4G] Execute
the Shield Hero right away!
[NAOFUMI]
How can this be happening?
I hate the Shield!
Come and take it off!
Damn it! Damn it all!
I just can't.
[RAPHTALIA groans, gasps]
[MYNE] It's about time
we set this poor girl free.
[NAOFUMI gasps]
[NAOFUMI]
Raphtalia...
[AULTCRAY]
Begin.
[NAOFUMI]
Wait!
[NAOFUMI gasps]
[MYNE]
There. You're free now.
Be grateful for
Sir Motoyasu's kindness.
[NAOFUMI]
Raphtalia...
This is goodbye.
[NAOFUMI gasping]
[yells]
[NAOFUMI gasps]
That's it... I'm done!
[groans]
[gasps]
I'll never be rid of it.
A messed up world
like this one...
[NAOFUMI]
...is not worth saving!
You're a liar and a cheat!
[MOTOYASU gasps]
Don't! Sir Motoyasu
set you free!
I never asked
anyone to free me.
I was with Naofumi by choice!
But wait a second.
I thought he was abusing you
and that he was
treating you badly.
You obviously know nothing
about Master Naofumi.
[MOTOYASU gasps]
[RAPHTALIA]
He never abused me
and he never made me do
anything I couldn't do!
He activated the curse when
I was too scared to fight.
He did it to protect both of us.
[MOTOYASU grunts]
And that's the problem!
Nobody should ever be
forced into a fight!
[RAPHTALIA] Master Naofumi
can't use any weapons!
The Shield defends,
so someone has to fight for him!
But you don't have
to be that person.
Don't you know he'll put
you in danger every time?
[RAPHTALIA]
Master Naofumi defends me!
We work as a team and he always
lets me rest when I'm tired!
No way. He just
isn't that kinda guy.
Well you should
think about this.
He was ready and willing to
help a sick, diseased slave
who was on the verge of death.
Master Naofumi fed me every
day--healthy, nourishing food.
Anything I wanted!
Not only that, he gave
me valuable medicines
and treatments,
and they cured my illness!
Are you capable
of such kindness?!
[MOTOYASU]
O-Of course I am.
[RAPHTALIA]
If that were true,
you'd have someone loyal
by your side, too,
instead of that
two-faced princess!
[MOTOYASU gasps]
--Excuse me...?
--How dare you say such things!
Take that back,
you damned demi-human!
[NOBLEMAN 4H]
Look, over there!
[gasps]
[NOBLEMAN 4I]
What's going on?
[NOBLEMAN 4J]
A fight?
Myne, sorry, but I have
to ask about your illegal,
and magical,
interference in the duel.
What are you talking about?
Illegal interference?
Hey, Motoyasu. Hate to say it,
but you lost that duel.
[MOTOYASU gasps]
Obviously someone shot a
powerful magic spell at Naofumi.
It was kind of hard to tell,
but it was clearly
a type of wind magic.
Uh, Myne?
I think you imagined it.
The audience didn't see a thing.
[ITSUKI] The king has told
everyone to keep quiet.
The nobles agree
there was foul play.
[REN] Wow, I can't
believe royalty would
interfere with a sacred duel.
[SPECTATORS whispering]
[RAPHTALIA]
Master Naofumi?
[NAOFUMI]
Why'd you come back?
You're free now.
[RAPHTALIA]
But I--
[NAOFUMI] I don't need
a traitor. Get lost.
I heard what they're saying...
They said you did
terrible things
and you forced yourself
on a member of your party
and lied about it.
[NAOFUMI gasps]
And yet I know now.
I believe that you would
never ever do such a thing.
[NAOFUMI]
I didn't do it!
Master Naofumi...
Just stay away!
Please, you have
to listen to me.
[NAOFUMI]
Don't touch me!
[gasps]
[NAOFUMI] Thanks to your
savior, Spear Hero Motoyasu,
you're free now.
Go! I never wanna see you again!
[RAPHTALIA gasps]
[NAOFUMI]
Or are you hanging around
just to get one last look
at the loser's face?
[RAPHTALIA]
Mm-mm.
[NAOFUMI]
Please, just leave me alone.
[RAPHTALIA] I believe you,
Master Naofumi. I really do.
Tell me... What can I do
to make you believe me?
[NAOFUMI]
"Believe you"?
After you betrayed me?
[RAPHTALIA]
I will always be on your side,
even if you never believe me.
[NAOFUMI]
Lies!
You're just saying that
to trick me again!
[RAPHTALIA]
No, I--
[NAOFUMI]
Shut up!
What else are you people
going to accuse me of?
From the moment I was brought
here, everyone despised me.
I tried, but it was over
before it started!
Nobody believes me.
This damn shield is a curse!
[NAOFUMI groans]
[NAOFUMI]
I hate it!
[NAOFUMI gasps]
I'm thankful.
This shield has saved
my life over and over.
[NAOFUMI gasps]
Don't you remember
during the Wave?
Even though you knew
you couldn't fight,
you still used your shield and
your strength to defend us all.
To be honest... I didn't do
any of that for the villagers.
But you must see that
it doesn't matter
and you still saved
all those lives.
[NAOFUMI]
Hey, I'm not that nice a guy.
Y'see, you were nothing
but a tool to use
for my own advantage.
I know, but it doesn't matter
because you still rescued me.
Stop it!
It was... all about how
I could save myself.
[gasps]
Master Naofumi, I bet I know
you better than anyone else
in this whole wide world.
I know how kind you are.
[RAPHTALIA] So even if the
whole world speaks ill of you,
I'll tell them they're wrong.
I'll defend you and remind
them of all you've done.
[RAPHTALIA] You're the one who
saved my life, gave me a sword,
and showed me that
I had a purpose in life.
[gasps]
I'll always be your sword.
And always be standing
beside you... no matter what.
[NAOFUMI]
I've always wished someone would
say those very words to me.
[NAOFUMI] I guess... I just
didn't hear her before.
I swear to be
your sword forever!
Wherever you go,
I'll be there with you.
[sobs]
This is a world where it's
hard to find people to trust,
but I know I can trust you.
'Cause you saved my
life, Master Naofumi.
I really do trust you.
[NAOFUMI gasps]
You're the Great Shield Hero.
[gasps]
Who... are you?
Don't you recognize me?
It's still me. I'm Raphtalia.
[NAOFUMI] But how? You don't
look like the same kid anymore.
[RAPHTALIA] Yes, and it's
time for you to stop
treating me like one, too.
I mean, sure, I might get
a little emotional sometimes...
...and act like a little kid...
I may be a burden, but...
But please. Please allow me
to still stand by your side.
[gasps]
[RAPHTALIA]
I need you and you need me.
We're a team.
[NAOFUMI sobbing]
[MOTOYASU growls]
I don't believe what's going on.
We all know it's wrong
for a hero to have a slave!
Or maybe... Raphtalia's
only doing this
because she's been brainwashed!
[REN]
I'm not so sure about that.
Just look at them.
It's not like a master
and a slave relationship.
It's different.
[RAPHTALIA] You've gone
through a lot of pain.
But from now on, you don't need
to be alone with the pain.
[NAOFUMI groans]
Huh?
[RAPHTALIA]
Good morning, Master Naofumi.
[NAOFUMI] Wow! Did you
make this all by yourself?
I did!
And it's all just leftovers that
I found in the castle kitchen.
Isn't it yummy?
Hey, Raphtalia,
is it really you?
Huh?
[NAOFUMI] Guess I need a little
time to get used to this.
It is sudden, but when
demi-humans level up
from being children,
we become instant grown-ups
in the blink of an eye.
[RAPHTALIA] That's why we are
seen as unnatural creatures,
always abused and
discriminated against.
[NAOFUMI]
I see.
[RAPHTALIA giggles] Hey, this
sandwich really does taste good!
[NAOFUMI gasps]
Is something wrong?
I can actually... taste it!
Let's make a deal
to eat lots of delicious
food from now on, okay?
[RAPHTALIA]
Master Naofumi?
[NAOFUMI]
Yeah?
[RAPHTALIA]
Let's do the best we can.