[RAPHTALIA panting]
[gasps]
[NAOFUMI grunts]
[RAPHTALIA grunts]
[NAOFUMI]
You okay?
Uh-huh.
[FILO yells]
[FILO]
Raphtalia, are you okay?
[RAPHTALIA]
Mm!
[NAOFUMI] I'm the one who
agreed to take this job.
You don't have to force
yourself to keep up.
[RAPHTALIA]
No, I'll be fine.
Master Naofumi, don't forget
I'm the one who begged
you to let me fight.
[NAOFUMI]
I know, but still...
We're almost finished, anyway.
[RAPHTALIA] Thank goodness
we managed to finish that job.
Aw, I wanted to fight
some more. I was having fun!
[NAOFUMI] We'll start heading
back to the capital tomorrow.
Huh? So you're wrapping up
the trading trip already?
[NAOFUMI] Yes, your
treatment takes priority.
We have to get to
the capitol's church.
We need some pretty powerful
holy water to dispel that curse.
But I...
We still have a long way.
You have to take it easy.
[RAPHTALIA]
Okay...
Raphtalia, I hope you
get better real soon!
Thanks, Filo.
I'm gonna be fine!
[FILO]
Good!
Huh?
Master, listen! Something's
going on over there.
[NAOFUMI]
Is that...?
[twig snaps]
[MELTY]
Uh?!
[filolials squawking]
[MELTY]
Uhh...
[NAOFUMI]
A human child?
In this empty void I
found the way to the light
Can't find my way
in this lingering world
Searching for the answer
the one that I can trust in
I'm just wandering around
Yeah, still stuck
in the shadow, ay
But I never follow that
This pain at last
Soon will pass
Turn into my own
unbeatable strength
This guy or that guy
dead or alive
by hiding alone we can't survive
I don't want to lie to myself
Keep on the fight, get right
I'll never lose and cry
Keep run up day and night
Time to rewrite
No matter what anyone say
I find my way, yeah
Never go away
Now, Nobody can stop me no way
I will make sure not to
forget those precious things
Yeah I'll take a stand
get back all that I've lost
Rise suddenly in this world
(I don't look back yeah)
This repetition will
repeat till the end
And the regrets are
still lingering in my head
Time to get it all back
now turn over
Rise suddenly in this world
(I don't look back yeah)
[filolials squawking]
Those birds looked yummy.
If we start now, we could
still hunt them down.
Huh? What do mean, yummy?
[FILO]
Hm?
[NAOFUMI sighs]
Now hang on just a second.
Those were filolials
just like you.
[FILO]
Like me...?
So big...
[BOTH]
Huh?
Are you really and
truly a filolial?
Do you mean me?
And you can actually
talk as well?!
[FILO]
Mm-hm.
[MELTY gasping]
I've always dreamed of
talking with a filolial
and here I am doing it!
Uhh...
Oh!
This is for you.
It's dried meat.
[FILO laughs]
Thanks!
[gasping]
[RAPHTALIA] Do you think
she's from the village?
No way. Too well dressed.
She's probably some
noble family's daughter.
[MELTY]
What's your name?
Filo, and you?
Filo's a beautiful name!
I'm Melty, Filo,
nice to meet you.
That's great, I'll call you Mel.
[gasping]
Ah! I forgot.
Would you like
some more of this?
[FILO]
I do! I do!
[RAPHTALIA] I've never seen
anyone love filolials like that.
Hey, Filo...
Don't forget we still have to go
to the village to do some work.
But in the meantime,
you can play with that girl.
You mean it?
Can she really?
Oh boy!
[MELTY]
Wow!
Can you really transform
whenever you want to?
Sure I can.
[MELTY]
Cool!
[NAOFUMI] She seems to have
taken that surprisingly well.
[RAPHTALIA] They certainly
seem to like each other.
Good, 'cause Filo needs to
spend time with other kids.
Master! Can I play for
a little while longer with Mel?
Just make sure you're
back by sunset.
Okay. Let's go.
And don't go too
far away, okay?!
[FILO]
'Kay!
[RAPHTALIA laughs]
Huh?
[NAOFUMI]
Now drink this slowly.
Thank you, Our Savior,
for saving him!
We're very thankful for you!
Master Naofumi. This woman
needs our help, too.
[NAOFUMI]
Sure.
[RAPHTALIA gasping]
Does it hurt a lot?
I'm fine. Don't worry about it.
I'm sorry. It's all my fault.
You promised not
to say that again.
[door creaks]
[FILO]
Master! I'm back!
Okay. We're glad you're back.
Are you all right, Raphtalia?
[RAPHTALIA]
Mm-hm.
I'm happy 'cause I made
such a wonderful friend today!
You mean that Mel girl
you met earlier?
[FILO] Mm-hm. She told
me she's traveled
to all sorts of amazing
places, just like me.
Uh-huh...
[FILO]
And then, she told me
about so much other
stuff I didn't know!
That so?
[FILO]
She also told me how she got
separated from the
rest of her people
while she was
playing with filolials.
Well, good for her...
Hm? Wait... separated?
[RAPHTALIA]
Master Naofumi...
Uh?
I apologize for
showing up so late.
Could you...
Um, would it be
a problem for me
to travel with you for
just a little while?
Wait a sec, you can't
travel with us.
[MELTY] I was on my way to
the royal capital and, um...
But then, when I saw all those
beautiful filolials, I, uh...
I was having so much fun
playing with them,
I got separated from my
bodyguards and left behind!
Bodyguards?
[MELTY]
Savior...
I hear you're leaving for
the capital tomorrow.
Would you please consider
taking me with you?
[NAOFUMI] She must've found out
about me from the villagers...
I realize it's a selfish
request, but you see...
I just...
I just have to return to
the capital right away!
I beg you!
[NAOFUMI] If she's a
nobleman's daughter,
we might get a reward,
but it could cause problems
if I'm the one
who takes her home.
Uh. Huh?
It's important, Master.
I really want you to help her.
[RAPHTALIA]
Master Naofumi...
We can't turn her away when
she's in trouble like that.
I want you to help her, too.
[NAOFUMI]
Uh--
[sighs]
Well, you're gonna have to
cough up a reward, y'know.
Of course, I'll ask my
father, he'll be glad to!
[FILO laughs]
We did it.
[MELTY giggles]
[VILLAGERS chattering]
[CHIEF 9A]
Our Savior,
we truly can't find
the words to thank you.
Yeah, well, I'd rather have
money than thank-yous.
The next time I come around,
I'll collect the
money you owe me.
[CHIEF 9A]
Oh, of course!
Okay, Filo...
[FILO]
Here we go!
[NAOFUMI]
Did I wake you?
No, no... I can keep watch now
if you want to go to sleep.
[NAOFUMI] It's fine.
You can sleep for tonight.
[RAPHTALIA]
They're both so quiet now.
Yeah, it's funny after all the
noise they were making earlier.
[RAPHTALIA]
Aren't you cold?
Not really.
[gasps]
We can't have you
catching a chill.
[RAPHTALIA]
Huh? Where's Mel?
[NAOFUMI]
Huh?
You don't think...
Uh-uh. There's no way.
I can't believe that Filo--!
[NAOFUMI]
Well, remember, she did say
even her own kind
looked yummy...
[RAPHTALIA]
Yes, but...
[NAOFUMI]
Raphtalia.
[RAPHTALIA]
Yes?
[NAOFUMI]
We saw nothing, okay?
[RAPHTALIA]
Wha--?! What are you saying?!
[NAOFUMI]
If we destroy the evidence...
[RAPHTALIA]
You can't be serious!
[NAOFUMI] What, you think it's
better for us to confess that
Filo ate some
nobleman's daughter?!
[FILO]
Is something wrong, Master?
Filo, what have you
done with Mel?
What do you mean?
She's sleeping in my feathers,
she has been all night long.
[NAOFUMI, RAPHTALIA]
Hm?
Time to wake up, Mel!
[gasps]
[BOTH gasp]
What's the matter?
[NAOFUMI]
What are you doing?
Filo's feathers are so
soft and comfortable
I couldn't resist
going to sleep...
[NAOFUMI]
So you took off your clothes?
[MELTY]
Mm-hm.
But how'd you get in there?
[RAPHTALIA gasps]
Unbelievable...
It's so nice and warm.
[NAOFUMI sighs]
Do these feathers have some
kind of sleep-inducing power?
[gasps]
[MELTY]
Well, then...
Uh?
I really can't
thank you all enough.
Master... Is it all right
if I take Mel home?
Okay, just make sure
you collect the reward.
'Kay. Let's go.
[MELTY]
Right.
Farewell till next time!
I think we'll miss her.
I'm sure we'll see her again.
Uh-huh.
[NAOFUMI] Why's the shield
the only one missing?
[NUNS chattering]
[NAOFUMI]
Hey. Lemme ask you something.
[NUNS]
His Holiness!
[POPE]
If it isn't the Shield Hero.
Welcome to our
humble church, my son.
I saw your magnificent
duel at the royal palace.
I must say, the way you fought
with the odds stacked against
you made a profound impression
on me, and I couldn't believe
you held your own despite
wielding only a shield.
[RAPHTALIA]
Master Naofumi...
Spare me the pleasantries.
I need the most
powerful holy water
you have to get rid of a curse.
Holy water, is that it?
[NAOFUMI]
Yeah.
Done. Then please
make your offering.
[NAOFUMI]
And that'd be...?
If you want the most powerful
one, that'll be one gold coin.
[NAOFUMI]
Fine by me.
[RAPHTALIA]
Master Naofumi, you mustn't!
That's too expensive!
I don't mind.
Compared to you, a gold coin
is worth absolutely nothing.
Master Naofumi...
[NAOFUMI]
You want a gold coin for that?
For what reason did you bring
the low-quality item, my dear?
Well, I mean, uh...
God is equally
compassionate to all.
If you did this to satisfy
your personal beliefs,
then you must repent.
I hope I have made myself clear.
[SISTER 9A]
I... I'm terribly sorry!
I apologize for my disciple.
No problem as long as
I get my money's worth.
I'm thankful for
your understanding.
[NAOFUMI]
That oughta do it.
Let's go.
[POPE] God will faithfully
show us the way to go.
Be grateful for his guidance.
Everything we have is given by
God's grace, never forget that.
Talk about patronizing.
Master Naofumi...
[NAOFUMI]
Hm?
[AKE panting]
Wait! Sh-Shield Hero!
Start running.
Huh?
But... But...
Why are we running?
What else can we do?
He's coming for us!
[gasps] Wait!
Boy, what a pest.
This way.
Are you feeling okay? Eh?
Uh-huh.
I think he's after me,
so let's split up.
That way he'll never
catch both of us.
But I...
Why don't you go get Filo.
Let's meet back at the carriage.
All right, I'll be there!
Hey, over here!
Wait, stop!
[NAOFUMI panting]
I sure hope I've...
lost him this time...
[MOTOYASU]
Naofumi!
[MOTOYASU yelling]
[CITIZENS chattering]
You're attacking me in
the middle of the street?!
What's wrong with you?!
Shut your face!
Where is that slave girl?
Free her now!
You're a real pain, y'know that?
Raphtalia isn't--
I'm not talking about her.
Huh?
[MOTOYASU] I'm talking
about the blonde girl
with wings on her back.
I saw her with you,
so don't lie to me.
Wait, Filo?
Filo's her name.
How can you make
her your slave?!
I've never seen a girl that
perfect. She's incredible.
It's hard to believe
there's a girl
who's just like Freon
from Hellworld.
[NAOFUMI]
Huh...?
Actually... I have
this thing for angels.
[NAOFUMI]
I don't care.
My heart has been in overdrive
ever since I got my first look
at that wonderful face.
I love other worlds!
And I love that
beautiful blonde angel!
This is ridiculous.
Hm?
[NAOFUMI laughs]
Dude, what's up with that?
Huh?
Oh, yeah. I almost forgot, that
fat bird's yours, too, isn't it.
I'm gonna send you and your
chubster friend both to hell!
Air Strike Javelin!
[NAOFUMI grunts]
[MOTOYASU]
Chaos Spear!
Knock it off!
What, are you crazy?
Yeah whattya doin',
fightin' here?
What's the big problem?
Come and get me!
Go ahead, say it again!
Just try it--!
[CROWD cheering]
[CITIZENS shouting]
Hey, Naofumi!
Wait! Spear Hero! You can't--
[MOTOYASU growls]
Wait a minute...
What's going on?
[AKE pants]
This is a public place!
Take your differences elsewhere.
This is no place for a duel!
[MYNE]
It is now.
[gasps]
[CROWD murmurs]
Surround them.
[DEPUTY CAPTAIN 3A sighs]
Draw swords, c'mon!
[gasps]
[MYNE]
Ladies and gentlemen,
I hereby declare this
an official duel between
the Spear Hero and
the Shield Hero.
All thanks to the royal crown
which has vested me
with the authority to do so.
[NAOFUMI growls]
[MELTY]
Put your weapons away!
[NAOFUMI, AKE gasp]
[KNIGHTS gasping]
I absolutely forbid the heroes
fighting amongst themselves.
What's this about?
What-- What are you
doing back here?
It has been way
too long... dear sister.
[gasps]
[MELTY] I hope you don't think
you or the hero's privilege
can cover up this mess.
The damage that has been done
is plain for everyone to see.
Spear Hero...
[MOTOYASU gasps]
[MELTY]
Look around you.
Would you call a man a hero
when he puts others'
lives at risk?
[MOTOYASU grunts]
[MELTY]
Dear sister,
your fun and games have
gone on much too long.
I have no idea what
you're talking about,
I'm simply doing my job as
the hero's aide, that's all.
Oh, so making him fight
in a public place
is your idea of aide, I see.
Do you dare to defy me,
your older sister?
[MELTY] If I have to, I will
let Mother know about this.
[growls]
[NAOFUMI]
Melty is Myne's little sister?
Is she's this country's...
[RAPHTALIA]
Master Naofumi!
What's going on here?
Nothing. Just Motoyasu again.
Uh, Filo.
That is what they call you,
isn't that right, my dear?
[FILO]
Mm-hm.
Oh, you poor thing. I'll bet
Naofumi's working you like
some sort of beast of burden.
But I like pulling
the carriage a lot.
[MOTOYASU] Naofumi,
you swine! How could you?!
You're making her pull your
wagon like that big fat bird?
You'll pay for this!
Why did you have to go
and call me fat like that?
Huh?
[FILO] You made fun of me
the last time we met, too.
I did? And when
was that? [gasps]
[MOTOYASU gasping]
[FILO]
I hate you, spear guy!
Uh... Y'mean you're
that... big fat--
[FILO grunts]
[MOTOYASU yelps]
[groaning]
Sir Motoyasu!
[crash]
Somebody get him to a doctor
right away and make it quick!
[KNIGHTS gasp]
[sighs]
Filo wins again!
A job well done.
I'm proud of you, Filo.
[FILO giggles]
Master Naofumi.
Come on, y'know he
had it comin' to him.
He always puts us through hell.
I know, but what's up with
that satisfied smirk?
[MELTY] Our Savior of
the Heavenly Fowl...
No. The Shield Hero
is your name.
I need to speak
with you urgently.
[ERHARDT] Uh, kid, would you
mind explaining what's going on?
[NAOFUMI]
It's a little complicated.
If you'd shut up we
could sort it out.
If you're gonna be here,
you gotta let me in
on the whole story.
Forgive me.
We couldn't think of
any other place closer.
[ERHARDT]
Oh boy...
So? Who exactly are you, anyway?
Please accept my apology.
I'm first in line to the
Melromarc throne, but I should
have told you that sooner.
The Second Princess.
I am Princess Melty Melromarc.
[ERHARDT]
The Princess...!
You're really in line
for the throne?
You're saying that you're gonna
be the next ruler, is that it?
But I don't understand
how you could be ahead
of your older sister
for the throne.
[MELTY] My sister has always
been a problem child
due to certain...
personality difficulties.
Not surprising.
I'm not lying.
I really had no idea
you were the Shield Hero.
But then... This might be
a perfect opportunity.
Opportunity?
It could be that...
[thud]
[BOTH gasp]
You can forget everything,
we're outta here.
I just can't trust
anything you say.
Huh?
[NAOFUMI]
Get lost.
[gasps]