[RAPHTALIA]
Master Naofumi...
Master Naofumi?
[NAOFUMI]
Mm?
Hey, we're here!
Whoa, look at that!
They changed it!
The crest has all
four heroes on it now.
This country'll sure be
different than it was before.
Uh-huh.
And we can finally
upgrade classes
now that we're not
outcasts anymore.
We can thank the queen for
that next time we see her.
Greetings! Long time no see.
The queen's entrusting
the dragon hourglass to us.
C'mon! Right this way.
[AKE]
We will now begin...
...the class upgrade ritual!
[FILO whines]
[RAPHTALIA sighs]
[MIRELIA]
I'm sorry,
was there a problem
with your class upgrades?
Kind of.
Thanks to you, we were
able to upgrade, but...
[BOTH]
Huh?
What--
That didn't take long.
Wow, this is incredible!
Huh?
[FILO]
Hey, what happened, Master?
[NAOFUMI]
What d'ya mean?
It wouldn't let me pick
the upgrade that I wanted.
Huh?
[RAPHTALIA] Same here.
I only got one option.
[NAOFUMI]
Hey, what's the deal here?
I, uh... That can't be right...
[FILO whines]
[MIRELIA] I have been
told that it's possible
for certain items to affect
the class upgrade process.
Perhaps that's what
happened to you.
[NAOFUMI] I wonder if the
cowlick Fitoria gave her
is the problem.
Hey!
[MIRELIA]
Fitoria?
You mean the Filolial Queen?
[MELTY] I wish you could've
been there to see her, Mother.
She looked
indescribably beautiful!
--[MIRELIA] Melty!
--Huh?
[MIRELIA]
Tell me more.
I want to know
everything about her!
[MELTY]
Well, in her bird form,
Fitoria was as big as the
monster we were fighting,
and some of her feathers
were the color of the sky!
[MIRELIA]
Anything else?
[MELTY]
She had feathers on her head
that were kind of like a crown.
And she let me
ride on top of her!
It was a dream come true!
[gasps]
It sounds wonderful!
I'm jealous of you. Truly!
To ride the Filolial Queen!
[NAOFUMI sighs]
Like mother, like daughter, huh?
[MIRELIA gasps, clears throat]
I'm sorry, excuse me.
[NAOFUMI] So why'd you
call us back here so soon?
Is something wrong?
Oh, no, I'm planning on
throwing a party tonight,
and I want all four of the
Cardinal Heroes in attendance.
I need advance notice
for that kind of thing.
[MIRELIA] If I'd told
you that was the reason,
you never would've come.
In truth, though,
the party's just an excuse
to get you all here.
There's something
you need to know.
Something all four of the
heroes would benefit from.
It is of the utmost importance.
Sorry about that.
I wish I could've given you
the class upgrades you wanted.
No, it's okay.
[NAOFUMI]
It's not.
I won't always be
around to help you.
I want to make sure you'll
be okay when I'm gone.
[gasps]
[COURT LADY 22A]
Pardon me, Sir Shield Hero.
We're ready for you.
[NAOFUMI]
We'll talk later.
Master Naofumi...
[NOBLES chattering]
I honestly wasn't expecting
to see you again so soon,
but I'm glad you're back, Filo!
Me, too, Mel!
Ooh! I have an idea.
Let's go explore
the castle later!
[MELTY]
Sure!
--[stomach growls]
--[FILO groans] I'm hungry...
What's taking Master so long?
[RAPHTALIA] Master Naofumi
had some important business
to attend to.
We should go ahead and eat.
'Kay!
Huh?
[sighs]
[NAOFUMI]
What's wrong with these guys?
[RAPHTALIA] If Master Naofumi
really is going to leave...
[gasps]
Ah look, it's a filthy demi.
So that's why my
wine tastes bad!
I don't care if you are
with the Shield Hero,
you demi's gotta
know your place!
Are you listening to me?!
Besides, we've got Itsuki!
Long as he's around, we don't
need any other heroes!
Especially not a disgrace
like the Shield! [hiccups]
You should tell that coward
he needs to get lost.
'Cause if he doesn't, he's gonna
wind up gettin' himself hurt.
Got that?
Who do you think's
going to get hurt first?
I bet it won't be him!
--[clattering]
--[NOBLES gasping]
[MAID 22A]
What's all that noise?
[MAID 22B] People are fighting
in the reception hall!
[MYNE giggles]
[MELTY]
Excuse me...
[MYNE gasps]
Now whose pie are you
poisoning there, Sister?
It's not yours, is it?
[chuckles]
I'd like to begin,
but none of you seem
very happy to be here.
Perhaps we should've had
dinner before the conference.
Did you ever really try to
make up with the other heroes?
Not this again.
Did you make any effort
to clear your name?
[sighs] Since we're
all here anyway,
why don't we have a
little heart-to-heart?
[ALL sigh]
Might as well get started.
It's no secret
the Three Heroes Church caused
a lot of trouble for you.
As leader of this country,
the fault of that is mine.
But Melromarc and
I would like to
make up for that
in any way we can.
And luckily,
Cal Mira Archipelago
appears to be activating.
--[ITSUKI gasps]
--Are you serious?
That means it'll generate
a bonus field, doesn't it?
"It's activating," huh?
It happens once a decade.
While activated,
all the experience points
adventurers gain in the area
are given a significant boost.
[MOTOYASU]
You're telling me you honestly
didn't even know that, Naofumi?
--[knocking]
--[MELTY] Excuse me.
Come in.
--[door opens]
--Huh?
[MIRELIA sighs]
I see now it's a good thing
we didn't go to
the party after all.
Malty--sorry...
Bitch was caught
trying to poison food
headed to The Shield
Hero's table.
[MOTOYASU]
What?! That's a lie!
My--I mean--
Whore would never do
something like that!
No. Siste--Bitch actually
admitted she was doing that,
thanks to her slave pact.
[MYNE screaming]
[MOTOYASU]
No, it can't be...
[MIRELIA] Sir Motoyasu,
you forged a slave pact
with her as well.
Why don't you confirm it for
yourself next time you see her?
[MOTOYASU groans]
Forget it. Can we
please just move on?
[MIRELIA] While my
daughter's foolishness
has clearly played
a significant part,
I believe the real reason you
heroes haven't leveled up faster
is the animosity between you.
Therefore, I believe it would be
prudent for you
to clear the air.
If you can all share what
you've learned with each other,
your trip to Cal Mira
will be much more efficient.
That seems unnecessary.
So what do you think
there is for us to share?
I already know
what I need to know.
We'd just be wasting time.
[NAOFUMI] Unbelievable. These
guys haven't learned anything.
[MIRELIA sighs] It seems as
though you've misunderstood me.
Perhaps I should
put this bluntly.
If nothing changes drastically,
Sir Naofumi may
survive the next Wave,
but the rest of you will not.
[ALL gasp]
But what do you mean by that?
[MIRELIA]
I'd have thought it was obvious.
The three of you were
defeated during the last Wave.
It's highly unlikely you'll
survive the next one.
[MIRELIA]
The only way you can win
is if all four heroes
rally together.
Think of this conference
as a way to cultivate
that solidarity.
[NAOFUMI]
The queen's absloutely right.
But can I really "rally
together" with these guys?
[ITSUKI]
All right.
Let's start with Naofumi.
[REN] Tell us how
you got your hands on
that cheat shield of yours.
[BOTH]
Uh--
[NAOFUMI]
Huh?
--[swords clanking]
--[KNIGHTS yelling]
[COMPANIONS grunt]
[RAPHTALIA]
I dare you to say that again!
[MALD]
I'll say it a thousand times!
Shield's weak!
A loser!
A waste of space!
You think you can
prove me wrong?
C'mere then! Give it a shot!
I understand how you're feeling,
but please calm down.
Don't worry,
I am perfectly calm.
Now calmly, I'll
dispose of this trash.
[ADVENTURER 22A gasps]
[groans] Guys!
The shield I'm using is
not some kind of cheat!
It's just the result
of hard work.
[NAOFUMI]
All right, fine.
I promise to tell you
everything I know...
...on one condition.
You have to tell me
your secrets first.
What do you think we should do?
We don't have much
of a choice, do we?
Okay, fine.
I'll keep it simple for ya!
When you pick up the
same type of weapon
as your legendary weapon,
you can make a copy
using the appropriately
named weapon copy system.
And it helped us when
we were starting out
'cause we got a bunch of
strong weapons for free.
Yeah.
[NAOFUMI]
Wait a second.
All you have to do
is pick it up?
Yup.
[ITSUKI chuckles]
Poor Naofumi.
It's funny you
didn't even know--
[NAOFUMI]
Just shut up and tell me how.
As long as you have the required
crafting skill and recipes,
you can feed your
weapon the materials,
and it'll automatically
craft items for you.
[NAOFUMI] You're kidding.
I've been doing it by hand!
[ITSUKI]
Really? What's wrong with you?
Oh, yeah. And there's
also a teleport skill.
You can instantly travel to
any location you've been before.
Don't tell me.
You didn't know about
that one either?
[NAOFUMI] Well, that would've
made life a lot easier.
[ITSUKI] Now for something
I'm sure you don't know:
the secret to getting
stronger as fast as possible.
Being the best in this world
all depends on how
rare your weapon is.
So if you focus on developing
weapons that are rare...
[REN]
Don't lie to him.
The key is weapon proficiency.
No, you're all wrong!
Refining your weapon
and boosting its stats
is what's important.
Are you crazy?
Weapons that are rare are
clearly much more valuable--
--[MIRELIA sighs]
--[REN] You're making that up.
It's not a factor.
[MOTOYASU] Right,
you have to refine a weapon
to make it stronger.
[ITSUKI]
That has nothing to do with it!
[MOTOYASU] Does, too!
Check the help screen!
[REN] My help screen
says nothing like that!
[sighs]
[KNIGHTS yelling]
--[MALD grunts]
--[RISHIA cries]
[BOTH grunt]
Everyone, please stop thi--
--[MALD groaning]
--[RAPHTALIA panting]
[REN] The two of you are
either liars or idiots.
[MOTOYASU]
What'd you say?
You heard me.
[ITSUKI]
You think you're cool,
but you're really nothing
more than a show-off!
--[REN] Draw your sword.
--[MOTOYASU] What?!
What a waste.
[ALL grunting]
Enough of this!
--And I'm the Bow--
--[ALL gasp]
This is pointless.
[RAPHTALIA]
Give it a rest!
That's it, I'm outta here!
[RAPHTALIA]
I'm so sorry.
I just couldn't stand listening
to him insult you like that.
Okay.
Things didn't go much
better for me either.
[BOTH sigh]
[NAOFUMI]
By the way, where's Filo?
[RAPHTALIA]
Asleep.
She wanted to spend the
night in Melty's room.
Those two have gotten
awfully close, haven't they?
[NAOFUMI chuckles]
Just a bit.
I wonder if... Huh...
[sighs] Yeah.
I don't see any weapon
copy system here.
[NAOFUMI] But... it didn't seem
like they were lying about it.
[NAOFUMI] Maybe the upgrade
methods they were talking about
were specific to their
legendary weapons.
Either way...
[NAOFUMI] I guess I'm just
gonna have to trust them.
[NAOFUMI gasps]
[NAOFUMI]
It's real!
Where are the other heroes?
[MIRELIA]
They left earlier this morning.
[NAOFUMI]
I was hoping to talk to them
about what I found last night.
Guess I'll do it later.
The ship you're taking
is docked in a harbor
that is far from here.
You should be on your way
as well, Sir Naofumi.
Right. We should get
going then, don't ya think?
--'Kay.
--Yeah.
[MIRELIA]
I wish you luck.
Thank you.
Naofumi.
[NAOFUMI]
Mm?
You better work hard out there
so you can level up
a whole bunch.
And here I was thinking
that you would go with them.
No.
Not my place.
Besides, I have
my own job to do.
Hey, kid.
How about that trial, huh?
I betcha feel great!
Uh... what are ya doin' there?
It worked!
What the-- "It worked," my ass!
You keep that up and you'll
completely run me
out of business!
How in the world
did you do that?
[FILO]
That's amazing!
That is not amazing,
it's called forgery or theft!
I'm sorry, but I have to.
[ERHARDT]
Wait, stop!
That one's expensive!
[ERHARDT gasps]
That one's really rare!
--[FILO giggles]
--Hey, hey, you put that down!
--[ERHARDT gasping]
--[RAPHTALIA] Try this!
--[FILO] I got one, too!
[ERHARDT]
Fine! Do whatever you want!
Are ya happy now?
Uh-huh.
I promise I'll pay you back.
Yeah, sure...
I'll just put it
all on your tab.
Now go make yourself
a killing in Cal Mira.
You got it.
[NAOFUMI] All righty,
that should cover everything.
--Master Naofumi?
--[NAOFUMI] Hm?
Could we maybe take a
little bit of a detour?
You're home.
That's good, Rifana.
[NAOFUMI] So... this is
Raphtalia's village.
[NAOFUMI] Were you the
ones who buried her?
[VAN]
Yes.
Everyone in the
village contributed.
[KEEL]
Hey, Raphtalia...
[RAPHTALIA]
Mm?
Let's make sure the village goes
back to how it used to be.
Yeah.
[VAN]
There must be more--
Survivors just like these two,
scattered throughout the world.
I'm sure there are many of them.
I only wish I knew how to help.
Is there something
I could do to help?
Huh...
[L'ARC]
Hey!
Uh--
[L'ARC] Do, uh...
Do you live around here?
Nah, I'm honestly
just passing through.
[L'ARC]
Gotcha.
What a sad sight, huh?
Whole place is
nothin' but rubble.
Bet it's the same where
you're from, kiddo.
Huh? Kiddo? You okay?
Hey, I'm not a "kiddo."
I'm actually 20.
[L'ARC]
Oh, sorry 'bout that.
That's kinda my
nickname for anybody
who looks younger than me.
Don't let it bug you.
L'Arc, we should be moving on.
[L'ARC]
Yeah, let's go.
We've got work to do.
--[THERESE] Yes.
--[NAOFUMI] Hm?
[L'ARC]
See ya!
[NAOFUMI]
Ready to go?
[RAPHTALIA]
Yeah.
I think I am ready.
I got to tell Mom, Dad,
and Rifana that I'm okay.
[NAOFUMI]
That's great.
What's wrong?
[RAPHTALIA]
Master Naofumi...
You won't... leave me, will you?
[RAPHTALIA]
Because I can't even imagine
living in a world
without you by my side.
[FILO gasps]
Wait a second.
Master, are you going somewhere?
You don't need to worry.
I'm staying right here.
You promise?
Of course.
Because I don't wanna
leave this world
in the hands of the
Three Cardinal Stooges.
Can we go now?
Yes!
[NAOFUMI] I can't leave until
these two find happiness here.
Master Naofumi?
Are you okay?
Yeah. I'm just fine.
[FILO]
Hey, Master, don't do that.
Tell us what you were
thinking about!
[NAOFUMI sighs]
Drop it. Let's go.
Aww... Why won't you tell us?
Filo, give it a rest.
[FILO]
At least I'm not a nag like you!
[gasps] When have I
ever "nagged" anyone?!
[FILO] Gee, I don't know,
let's think...
[RAPHTALIA]
Ugh, Filo, quit messing around.
You're bothering Master Naofumi.
[FILO]
Nuh-uh! I am not!
[RAPHTALIA]
Uh-huh, you are, too!
[FILO] I don't bother him
half as much as you do!
[RAPHTALIA]
Is that the ship we're taking?
[ADVENTURERS chattering]
Only so many ships
set sail in a day.
Those morons, look at 'em!
Can we go, Master Naofumi?
Go ahead.
[CAPTAIN 22A]
We're terribly sorry, sir!
We thought we had a private
room prepared for you, but...
...the other heroes got
here early and they...
...took over pretty
much every cabin.
[NAOFUMI] Punishing us
for making them wait?
[RAPHTALIA]
That doesn't bode well, does it?
Sorry for the inconvenience,
but you'll be sharing this
room with other passengers.
[NAOFUMI]
Fine.
[knocking]
[L'ARC]
Come in.
[gasps]
Oh! Hey, kiddo!
We meet again, huh?