[HARUKA]
Ikuya?
--[HARUKA gasps]
--[ASAHI] Huh?
[ASAHI]
He's here?
Where's he going? Hey, wait up!
Excuse me, you guys,
it's an emergency!
[IKUYA] Why do you have
to quit swimming, Haru?
[ASAHI panting]
Damn it, we lost him.
Ikuya.
[TEAMMATES]
Go!
Ikuya!
[MAKOTO]
Even Ikuya's getting beaten!
How'd this happen?
[TEAMMATES]
Asahi!
[MAKOTO]
Wow.
The competition's
tougher at regionals!
Look at that.
He got faster again.
[GROUP]
Haru!
[ASAHI laughs]
He is so great!
Go, Haru!
[ASAHI]
Go!
[ASAHI] Crap! We were
so close to victory!
Yeah, and we tried so hard, too.
But it still wasn't
enough, was it?
We're just gonna have to
practice more from now on!
Yeah, you're right.
It's fine. We'll win the
next summer tournament.
The four of us!
Heck yeah!
Let's start our swimming
boot camp! Right now!
[MAKOTO]
Hold on--slow down, Asahi!
Don't you think it's a little
too early for all that?
[ASAHI]
Yeah, well, I can't help it!
I'm so pissed off
about losing today,
I wanna get to work
as fast as I can!
[HARUKA grunts] I told you,
I only swim free.
[IKUYA]
He even says it in his sleep.
[ASAHI whispering]
We should whisper stuff
and see if it messes
with his dream!
[MAKOTO] Can't we just wake
him up normally, please?
[ASAHI]
Aw, that's no fun!
Okay, fine, you won't
let me do that,
so how about I just tickle
him until he goes crazy?
[MAKOTO]
Asahi, that's enough, okay?
[ASAHI]
Got ya now, Ikuya!
[HARUKA]
What's going on?
Well, we came to get you.
It's time for training camp!
Yeah! We talked
about that, remember?
We decided to camp out at the
school, just the four of us!
I already put in for
permission and everything!
And it's even okay
with my brother.
[MAKOTO]
Good swim. Here.
Thank you.
[MAKOTO] Hey, look at
that. Check out Ikuya.
[HARUKA]
Free.
Whoa! That's so cool!
Ikuya's doing freestyle?
Look at him go!
I'm not gonna let him
outdo me, though!
A training camp?
That sounds ambitious.
Uh-huh.
They wanna be ready
for next summer.
That's an early start.
Better than a late one.
I've got an idea.
Why don't we bring
them some snacks?
[sighs] We have to try
not to spoil them too much.
[GUARD 2A] Well, I'm here
if you boys need me.
Okay, thanks a lot, sir!
[IKUYA]
Don't fall asleep, Asahi.
[yelps] What? No, I'm awake!
Hey, it's too early for that.
We're just gettin' started!
It looks like the next
thing on the agenda
is reflex training, then
weightlifting before bed.
And practice is at sunrise.
That's way too much work!
Weren't you the one who planned
everything out for us?
Not that this thing
makes sense, anyway.
You didn't even schedule
a single break in here.
What do you mean, "break"?
We can't expect to win
the next summer tournament
if we're sitting around
on our butts all the time!
That's a long way off.
You better not pile
all this work on us
and then transfer away
to another school again.
Oh, yeah, that's a good point.
Your family tends to
move around quite a bit.
Guess it comes with the
territory with your dad's job.
No need to worry!
I'm not gonna move ever again!
And besides, we'll never
get anything done
if we keep focusing on
dumb stuff like that!
The best thing for us to do
is just live life in the now!
[stomach growls]
[MAKOTO laughs]
Somebody's hungry!
[HARUKA]
Let's eat something.
Yes! Dibs on chicken sandwich!
[IKUYA]
What? Hey, that's not fair!
We only have one
of those things!
[ASAHI]
You snooze, you lose!
[MAKOTO]
Don't fight!
[ASAHI snoring]
Huh?
Where's my towel?
Ikuya.
--[HARUKA] What're you doing?
--[gasps]
I thought you were all sleeping.
I woke up, and then came
to get something that I left.
Look up.
Huh?
On the news, it said
there's gonna be
a meteor shower tonight.
[HARUKA] Oh, yeah, I heard
something about that.
[IKUYA] Hey. Have you ever
wished on a shooting star?
'Course not. When
you want things,
you have to make them happen.
[laughs] That's so you.
[HARUKA] Anyway.
You swam freestyle today.
Yeah. I started thinking that
maybe I ought to give it a try.
I mean, we lost the medley
at the tournament,
but your freestyle
was so incredible.
You passed those guys
like it was nothing.
Haru.
All I want is to learn
how to swim like you do!
Well, thanks, but,
just copying my form
won't be enough.
The point of swimming freestyle
is to do it your way.
I know that. But still.
I'll work hard and
improve my speed.
So, um!
Please, Haru.
Promise me we'll race
freestyle someday!
Sure.
[IKUYA gasps]
[HARUKA]
It's happening.
So, what did you wish for?
[IKUYA]
It's a secret.
[ASAHI]
Well?
[HARUKA]
He's not here.
[ASAHI sighs]
Maybe we had the wrong guy.
No. I know that was Ikuya.
Haru and Asahi should've
been back by now.
I wonder if something's wrong.
[phone buzzes]
[KISUMI]
What's up?
Dunno. It's from Nagisa.
[MAKOTO] Apparently,
Ikuya's still swimming!
Nagisa thinks he might even
be at this tournament!
[gasps] Ikuya's here?
[NAGISA]
I wonder if Haru and Mako
got to see their old friend.
Sorry, is Haru the guy
who was all dressed up
and riding a camel in the
recruiting video we saw?
[NAGISA laughs]
That's him!
The mysterious peddler
on his trusty camel, Chappy!
[SHIZURU]
Wow!
And now he's working hard
at a college in Tokyo.
He's in Tokyo? Wow,
that's so awesome!
Oh, that's right,
Romio, you transferred
from Tokyo, didn't you?
Uh-huh!
Well, I was actually
born in New York,
but my second home is Tokyo!
So when are we gonna get
to ride Chappy the camel?
Easy there.
Chappy's a worthy goal,
but the summer tournament
has to come first.
Oh, yeah, speaking of Tokyo--
that's where the nationals
are being held this year,
so if we make it there,
you'll get to meet
Haru and Mako yourselves!
But wait a sec.
If you guys get to compete
at the All-Japan Invitational,
wouldn't that mean you'll
have an opportunity
to swim with Haruka again there?
Hold on, we can swim at that?
[AYUMU]
Yes. There's no age restriction,
so even high school
students can compete.
If you want to go,
all you have to do is beat
a certain qualifying time, and
you're automatically eligible.
I see. Well, you know,
it's a lofty dream,
but every little step
gets us closer!
We can start by knocking out
our special practice regimen!
Let's give it our all,
Iwatobi Swim Club!
[IWATOBI SWIM CLUB]
Yeah!
[MAKOTO] Let's see here.
Where's Ikuya's name?
[gasps]
[MAKOTO] There! It's under
Shimogami University.
According to the program,
he's only gonna do the IM.
"IM"?
It means "Individual Medley."
So he's not swimming
relays anymore.
But he's at Shimogami.
I hear they're a really
strong sports school.
[AZUMA]
Shimo U is home
to a slew of uniquely
talented athletes.
Hah. That's their section there.
Watch out for those guys.
[SAGAE]
Whoa. A new record.
Plenty of strong
competitors this year, huh?
Heh. You seem glad.
Sure!
It's always exciting
to watch a fast swimmer.
Right, Kirishima?
Who cares? I focus on me.
There's no reason to compare
myself to anybody else.
I'm gonna go get ready.
[HIYORI]
Good luck!
Why is that guy
always so standoffish?
[MAKOTO]
Um, excuse me.
Is there an Ikuya
Kirishima here with you?
Sorry, who are you people?
We are some of Ikuya's old
buddies from middle school.
Oh, you were that
super-fast kid!
Who swam the 100-meter free!
[TERASHIMA] Haruka Nanase
from Iwatobi, right?
--Yeah.
--[ASAHI] Hey, I know you!
You're Kotarou Terashima, right?
Wha...?
[ASAHI]
AKA, the Archerfish of Naruto!
Why is he an "Archerfish"?
Don't you ever
call me that again!
[yelps]
Asahi!
[SAGAE laughs]
Well, that may be his alias,
but you shouldn't
say it to his face.
You should be happy that
you even have an alias!
I decided to start
calling myself
"The Marlin of Genkainada,"
but it didn't stick,
and now I'm the only person
who ever uses it!
Ugh, what a loser.
What'd you say?
There's nothing lamer
than giving yourself
an alias, nerd.
Just let it go, Asahi--
we didn't come here
to pick a fight!
So, is Ikuya with you or not?
[HIYORI]
Obviously, he's not.
Don't see him anywhere, do you?
Anyway, the next race is
getting ready to start.
I suggest you go back
to your own seats,
so you can cheer them on.
[ASAHI]
Wow, Haru's unbelievable!
[gasps]
[ASAHI] He beat his personal
record time again!
[IKUYA] Right. I need
to get stronger, too.
It looks like Ikuya's
working extra hard today.
Yeah.
[NATSUYA] All right, practice
is over! Time to cool down!
Hey. We're all done for the day.
[panting]
You okay?
I'm fine. Just gonna
swim a bit more.
[ASAHI]
Uh, wait a sec!
[GUY 2A]
Good practice.
[GIRL 2A]
Yeah, you, too!
[IKUYA] Stronger. I have to
become as strong as I can!
Just like Haru.
[IKUYA gasps]
[ASAHI]
Something's not right with him.
[IKUYA]
I feel so... heavy.
Ikuya! He sank!
[BOTH gasp]
You're okay!
Oh, thank goodness!
You almost drowned.
So we brought you
to the hospital.
Haru dove in and saved you
in the nick of time!
Yeah.
Sorry.
[NATSUYA]
Look. This all happened
because you pushed
yourself too hard
and didn't take any breaks!
You're lucky to be alive.
A few more seconds
and you could've died!
[NAO] Natsuya, you don't
have to be so hard on him.
No, it's okay.
Thank you for saving me.
Sure thing. I'm glad
you're all right.
[NATSUYA] They're gonna keep you
here a while just to be safe.
Don't you ever do
something like that again!
[IKUYA]
I'm sorry.
You guys missed out on
practice because of me.
[HARUKA]
It's fine.
[IKUYA] But that was our last
chance to swim this year.
Just means we'll have
to put our goals on hold
till next summer, that's all.
Till next summer, huh?
I swear. I'll get
stronger by then.
For the team, and for myself.
I'll even be good enough
to compete against you.
That said.
[gasps]
[IKUYA] Promise me something.
That next summer
you'll race me freestyle.
[HARUKA]
Okay. You got it.
What's with that glasses
guy from Shimo U?
Why's he gotta act
like such a jerk?
And still no Ikuya, either.
I know.
Then again, we were the ones
who went over and butted in.
[ANNOUNCER 2A] ...men's
200-meter individual medley
--are preparing to swim.
--Look. The IM's starting.
[MAKOTO]
Ikuya's heat.
[ASAHI]
There he is.
[whistle blows]
[ANNOUNCER 1A]
Take your marks.
--[beep]
--[CROWD] Go!
He's fast!
What a butterfly!
[MAKOTO]
His strokes are strong.
I don't remember him
being this powerful.
[HIYORI]
Keep it up, Ikuya.
Good work. This just
might be a record.
[ASAHI]
That's Haru's freestyle.
His strokes do seem
to have a similar rhythm,
but still. It's not just a copy.
[gasps]
[KISUMI]
What changed?
I thought back in middle school,
Ikuya used to swim breaststroke
more than anything.
Yeah. That was his specialty.
During our first summer,
he told me he wanted
to get better at free.
Not just freestyle.
It looks like he's also mastered
the backstroke and butterfly.
[AZUMA] Hey. Why do you
only swim freestyle?
Huh? This guy?
[AZUMA] What's wrong?
S'that all you wanna do?
[HARUKA]
Uh--
[AZUMA] Well, I'll let
you give it some thought.
Okay that was weird.
What's his deal?
No clue.
Maybe he's a scout
or a coach or something.
I guess that could be it.
Crap! We forgot about Ikuya!
[MAKOTO]
Locker room?
[ASAHI]
Yeah, this way!
No luck.
Well, his race hasn't
been over that long.
Maybe we should wait in
here for a few minutes?
[KISUMI] Now we're getting
into stalker territory, guys.
There you are.
Hey.
'Bout ready to take off?
What's the big hurry?
Relax, the tournament's
not even over yet.
Our school races are the
only ones that matter, right?
Here. I brought all
your stuff for ya.
Yeah, I dunno.
We should ditch this place
and go get somethin' to eat.
Come on, I'll let
everybody else know
that we're leavin' early.
[IKUYA]
Uh...
So, your 200-meter backstroke.
It was faster today.
Yeah, but it's nowhere
near as fast as yours.
Seriously, you did
some amazing work
out there today, Ikuya!
You should let Natsuya know
the first chance you get.
He's in another time zone.
It's not like it's urgent news.
Sure, sure. Hey, why don't
you order this cake!
It's got pistachio cream,
your favorite.
Maybe I'll get one, too.
Uh, Hiyori. You're
acting kind of weird.
Oh, come on, I'm always
weird, you know that!
[MAKOTO sighs]
We didn't even get to say hi.
[KISUMI] He's not avoiding
us on purpose, is he?
[laughs] No way!
Well, I would've liked to
catch up with him, too,
but at least we found out
that he's still swimming.
I mean, that's enough for--
[yelps]
[KISUMI]
Are you all right?
[MAKOTO]
Sorry, I only have tissues.
[ASAHI] Oh, thanks.
Ugh, now I'm all sticky.
[HARUKA] I think I left
my towel at the venue.
[MAKOTO, ASAHI]
Huh?
[HARUKA]
I'll go get it.
[MAKOTO] 'Kay. We'll wait
for you at the station!
Cool.
[HIYORI]
Somethin' wrong?
[IKUYA] I think I left
my phone at that café.
Then let's go back.
[IKUYA]
No. I can go by myself.
See ya tomorrow.
[HIYORI]
Forgot your phone, huh?
That's not all you've forgotten.
[gasps]
Ikuya.
Haru.
[HARUKA]
I saw your individual medley.
[IKUYA]
Oh, you were there?
I didn't see you swim any races.
Why did you only
compete in the IM?
Do you not do relays anymore?
[IKUYA]
What for?
I'm fine swimming alone.
[gasps]
[HARUKA]
Back in middle school...
When I quit out of nowhere...
I shouldn't have.
I'm sorry, I just--
[IKUYA]
Forget about that.
It doesn't bother me now.
It's all in the past.
"All in the past"?
[HIYORI]
Hey, there you are!
Hiyori?
I'm okay, you could've
gone home without me.
Yeah, sorry, I know.
I just had a little
spark of curiosity.
Nanase, was it?
Ikuya's pretty exhausted
from his big race,
so I'd prefer you didn't
keep him too long, okay?
Come on. Let's go.
Wait a sec--
[ASAHI]
No way!
Maybe that means
he really is angry!
[sighs] You know,
when I moved away,
I also had to quit the
team without warning,
so I guess I can't
really blame him.
I prob'ly owe him
an apology, too.
Well, at least we know
where to find him now.
Why don't we all go visit
him together sometime?
That way, you can tell him
what's on your mind.
[ASAHI]
Good thinkin'. Let's do that.
[NATSUYA] Hey, Ikuya! How was
the newcomer tournament?
Uneventful. I'm surprised
you're awake.
[NATSUYA]
Why wouldn't I be?
It's evening where I am, too.
Oh, and I guess I did
get a little bit of sleep
during the flight.
[IKUYA]
Hm? You're not in America?
[NATSUYA] Nah, I heard about
this interesting coach,
so I flew out to meet him.
I'm in Sydney.
Just landed a minute ago.
[NAGISA]
Wonder how Rin's doing?
[REI] The lives of two men
with complex thoughts
and feelings are about to cross!
[NAGISA] Next time:
"Fist Swim in Another Country!"
[REI]
Don't miss this one!