[HARUKA]
Water is alive.
I can't imagine how many times
I've had that thought.
[HARUKA]
Water's a living thing.
No matter how much your
body grows and changes,
the water'll always reach
out and embrace you.
It's got a mind of its own.
But...
[HARUKA]
How long can that last?
It's not just about water,
there's one other thought
that's always stuck with me.
[gasps]
[HARUKA]
Prodigy at ten.
Genius at 15.
At 20, I'll be...
[HARUKA]
Makoto.
Hey, Haruka. G'morning!
[MAKOTO]
Whoa!
Aw. Not cool, Haru!
You came here to swim, right?
Uh, well, yeah, but...
[MAKOTO chuckles]
I swear. Sometimes it seems like
you can't survive
out of water, Haruka.
[HARUKA]
Don't call me Haruka.
[MAKOTO] In high school,
you always used to talk about
how you couldn't wait
to be a normal person.
Do you still feel
the same way these days?
Well, uh...
[MAKOTO gasps]
I gotta run!
See ya 'round, Haru!
And best of luck today!
Thanks.
A normal person. Right.
[IKUYA] I'm never gonna
be a normal person.
[HIYORI]
Huh? Where'd that come from?
[IKUYA]
Nevermind. It's just a saying.
No need to worry about that.
You are extraordinary
and you always will be.
You are Ikuya, after all.
Are you sure that's
a good thing?
'Course it is! What's
wrong? Are you mad?
I'm fine.
[DAVID]
Oi, Rin, ya done?
Nah, I'm gonna swim
a little longer.
[DAVID]
Okay. Have fun then.
Yeah, thanks, I'll
see you tomorrow.
[RIN laughs] Oh, man, those
goofballs never change.
[ASAHI gasps]
Hang on. Don't I know you?
Nanase? Haruka Nanase?
You do remember me, right?
It was a long time ago, but...
[gasps]
[HARUKA]
Wait. Yeah, Asahi Shiina!
Aw, I knew you couldn't
forget this face!
It's been a hot minute.
I don't think I've seen you
since we were in middle school!
This is too crazy!
How come you don't look all
that excited to see me?
I guess that's just par for
the course with you, huh?
You haven't changed much!
Well, neither have you.
Sorry, but that's
where you're wrong.
Can't you tell how
mature I've gotten?
By the way, guess what!
You remember Kisumi
Shigino, don't you?
He's going to this college, too!
Yeah, I knew that.
Aw, man, I wanted to tell you!
So, did you guys go to high
school together, or what?
Nope. Different schools.
His younger brother
takes swimming lessons
at the Iwatobi SC though.
So I saw him again there.
SC?
[HARUKA] Anyway, you
still swimming, Asahi?
Uh-- Well, yeah,
why wouldn't I be?
In fact, starting
practice here today.
What about you though?
Didn't you quit doing
Swim Club after I moved?
You never answered
my letters, so...
[HARUKA]
Sorry.
But, yeah, I started
swimming again
after I got to high school.
I'm headed to practice now, too.
Wow, really? That's awesome.
I can't wait to compete on
the same team as you again!
Same here.
[ASAHI chuckles]
[TSUKAMOTO]
Listen carefully, first-years.
My name's Coach Tsukmoto.
Welcome to your first
swim team practice with us.
Let me make one thing clear.
You're not gonna have time
for your typical college
shenanigans here.
You'll be way too busy for
part-time jobs and partying.
Stay focused at all times!
Now then.
I want all our newcomers
to introduce themselves
one at a time and demonstrate
their best stroke for us.
Come on, line up!
[SWIM TEAM]
Yes, sir!
[RIN grunts]
[WILSON]
Ah, Rin, you're still here.
Good timing, actually.
[RIN]
Hey there, Coach.
I want to introduce somebody.
Rin, this is my
good friend, Mikhail.
Konnichiwa , Rin- kun .
Wil has told me a
great deal about you.
"Rin- kun "?
[WILSON]
He's lived in Japan.
You've got some
impressive muscles there!
Oh so glad to meet
you, Mr. Matsuoka.
Uh. Yeah, nice to meet you, too.
[TSUKAMOTO]
Next!
I swim freestyle.
My name's Haruka Nanase.
[ASAHI]
Hey, Haru.
You still goin' around
sayin' you only swim free?
[HARUKA] No. I'll do
other strokes at practice.
But...
When I swim for real,
I swim free.
[ASAHI laughs]
Haru's still got it!
How 'bout that?
[panting]
Rin- kun , cho-very good!
I'm sorry, what did you say?
It's Japanese slang
for "really amazing"!
[ASAHI]
Speeding up on the turn!
[MIKOSHIBA]
That's a nice kick!
[laughs]
[BOTH gasp]
[SWIM TEAM gasps]
[SUZUKI]
Great work, Nanase!
Yeah, you know.
I saw you swim free
before, at nationals.
I got to go last year.
No way!
You didn't tell me you
went to nationals, Haru!
Our team almost
qualified to go, too,
but we just barely missed out.
Oh, that's too bad.
I was at nationals last year.
Swam the 200 free.
Name's Isana Kiryuu.
And I'm Hikaru Unita.
Came here from Hokkaido.
He's our guy.
Everybody calls him the
King Salmon of the North.
Stop fishin' for compliments!
Oh, that's cool, I guess.
[HIKARU] Come on,
you're supposed to laugh!
Listen, first-years,
college is a whole different
animal than high school.
Don't get careless.
[BOTH]
Uh, yes, sir!
And don't forget,
the newcomer
tournament's next week.
The first-years from all the
best college teams in Kanto
are gonna be there,
so I want all of you
to bring your A-game!
[TSUKAMOTO]
Mikoshiba, c'mere!
Yes, sir, Coach. Coming!
From the looks of it,
Mikoshiba's swimming style's
all about raw power.
I've watched him
in tournament races.
Oh, yeah, you and
Mikoshiba already
know each other, right, Haru?
Yeah, we do.
We went to different
high schools, though.
Hey, I was wondering.
Where's Makoto?
D'you know if he's doing okay?
He's living in Tokyo now, too.
[SAOTOME]
Oh, gosh.
I really hope I'll be able
to keep up with this lecture.
If you want, I could
let you borrow my notes.
Would you?
--Sure. Uh-- Oh.
--[phone buzzes]
Who's Nagisa?
Is that your girlfriend
or something?
No, he's actually a guy
I used to swim with
in high school.
[NAGISA]
Whoa! Mako replies really fast!
[GOU] Sure it's okay to
bug him? He might be in class.
[REI] I don't think Makoto's
the type of person
who would reply to a text
message during a lecture.
[gasps]
[NAGISA]
What, is that all?
[REI] All you said
was that we'd acquired
three new members.
He probably didn't know how
else to respond to that.
Okay, then we'll just
have to give him
some more information, yeah?
Come over here, you three.
We need to take a
quick photo of you!
[ROMIO, SHIZURU, AYUMU]
Oh! Okay!
[NAGISA]
Let's start with you, Romi!
Gimme a big smile!
[NAGISA]
Shizu, you're up next!
[REI]
Come on now, don't be so rigid!
[NAGISA]
Now you, Ayumu!
[GOU] You know you can
relax a little, right?
Um, okay.
So, Ayumu, if you had to
pick a favorite muscle,
which one would it be?
Oh, uh. I'm not really
that into muscles.
What, who doesn't like muscle?
[AYUMU]
I don't mind them, but I prefer
people with a little
fat on them.
This might not be the
right club for you!
[REI]
Oh, dear.
Is it me, or do these
look like mugshots?
Yeah, they kinda do.
Then why don't we
take one together!
Come on, guys, get
into your swimsuits!
I have to say, it's a
little bit strange
that I'm the one you're
asking to take your picture.
But all right!
I'll make sure it's the best
group photograph you ever saw!
As the saying goes.
"Only a mortal can
capture a photograph
that's fit for the gods."
"Miracles don't--"
[NAGISA] Sorry, Miss A,
we don't have all day!
[AMAKATA]
Ah! Okay!
Now, pay very close attention.
Photography theory
tells us that if we--
[camera clicks]
[GOU]
Ha! You were saying, Mr. Expert?
That is far from beautiful.
Get back together so we
can take another one--
[NAGISA]
Okay, and off it goes!
[yelps] No!
[GOU]
It's so you!
[REI]
What is that supposed to mean?
[MAKOTO chuckles]
That's our Rei.
[phone buzzes]
[MAKOTO]
Haru?
[VOICE]
Hey, Makoto, it's me.
Huh? That isn't Haruka's voice.
[ASAHI]
Aw, man, he didn't buy it!
Who is this? Is Haru
there with you?
Sure is, and Kisumi's
with us, too!
With who?
[KISUMI] Hey, Makoto!
That musta been weird.
You were expecting
Haru and got Asahi.
Hey! Dammit, Kisumi.
Why'd you hafta go and let
the cat out of the bag?
Asahi? Wait, you
mean that Asahi?
Yep, the one and only.
Did you miss me?
[MAKOTO] So your sister runs
this whole restaurant?
[AKANE] Well, it originally
belonged to my mother-in-law.
She managed it for a long time.
[ASAHI] Yeah, so now Akane
basically owns the place.
Whatever you want,
it's on the house.
Wait, I'm sorry, but you
do have to pay your bill.
Aw, come on, sis.
There's no need to be stingy.
[AKANE]
I have to! This is a business.
Anyway, Makoto,
you sure look like
you've grown a lot since
last time I saw you.
Oh, yeah, he's a big man now!
Thanks. But you've
changed, too, Asahi.
Like, your face looks older.
Not too old, right?
Oh, hey, Haru says that
you've decided on your major.
Sports education
sounds interesting.
So, you wanna be a
swimming teacher, then?
Yeah, I figured
teaching kids how fun
swimming is would be
the perfect job for me.
He's right, sounds
just like him.
If I remember right,
you moved to Kyushu
after you left
Iwatobi, didn't you?
Were you able to keep swimming?
[ASAHI] Yeah, for a while,
but then I transferred
to Kazami High School
not too long after that,
and they didn't have a
swim club when I got there.
Can you believe it?
It took a lot of doing,
but I managed to rustle up
enough members to start
a club on my own.
[MAKOTO] Wow, you, too?
That's what we did!
We started Iwatobi Swim Club
with some friends.
Tell him about it.
Yeah. First we had to
fix up the pool, though.
[ASAHI]
Really? So did we!
That's a lot harder work
than I thought it'd be.
It took us forever to scrub
all that moss out!
Ooh, wanna see some pictures?
What, of the moss?
[ASAHI]
No, genius!
[ASAHI] See? These are my
old buddies from high school.
[KISUMI]
Huh.
And this is a picture of my
old swim team from Kyushu.
We kicked major butt at
the junior tournament.
[KISUMI]
Eighth grade?
[ASAHI]
Ninth grade, I think.
Oh, then there's this one.
[gasps] Look, I'm so little!
[KISUMI laughs] Look how
young and innocent Haru is!
I'm still young and innocent.
That's a weird thing to say.
You look like a monkey, Asahi.
Hey! You take that back!
Wait a sec! There's Ikuya!
Wonder what he's been up to.
Uh-oh. Something wrong?
Not really, it's just
that I never got a chance
to tell Ikuya I was moving
away before I left Iwatobi.
Well, uh...
He actually followed
Natsuya to America
from eighth grade up.
I'm not sure if he's still
doing any swimming, though.
We'll never make
friends like we had
back then, that's for sure.
Hey, that almost sounded
like a line out of a movie!
What are you tryin' to sound
all cool and stuff for?
And why do you have to
talk about "back then"
like it's ancient history?
We're still friends now,
aren't we? Ya big dope.
[AKANE]
Reel it in, you two.
You guys're way too young
to sit here reminiscing
like you're a bunch
of old geezers.
You need to enjoy your youth
while you've got it.
Know what I mean?
Ha! Guess you're right.
Yeah, we need to
live in the present.
Which is why we gotta
roll up our sleeves
and aim for the big leagues now!
True, that's one way
you could do it.
Well, you wanna make it big?
Then first you have to win
the All-Japan Invitational
and get onto the national team.
And before any of that,
there's the newcomer
tournament, too.
[AKANE]
Oh, you're talking about the
Intercollegiate Newcomer
Swimming Tournament, right?
My husband's supposed
to be covering that.
"Covering"?
Oh, yeah, she's married
to a sports journalist.
Sounds like a cool
job, doesn't it?
[KISUMI]
Whoa, that's amazing!
[MAKOTO] So that's why
there are so many pictures
and news articles
hanging up in here.
[ASAHI]
Uh-huh!
Funny enough, after
that last tournament...
Ikuya!
[ALL]
Haru!
[ASAHI] Crap! We were
so close to victory!
Yeah, and we tried
so hard, too.
But it still wasn't
enough, was it?
We're just gonna have to
practice more from now on!
Yeah. You're right.
It's fine--we'll win the
next summer tournament.
The four of us.
[ASAHI]
Heck yeah!
Let's start our
swimming boot camp!
Right now!
[MAKOTO]
Hold on, slow down, Asahi!
Don't you think it's a little
too early for all that?
[ASAHI]
Yeah, well, I can't help it!
I'm so pissed off
about losing today,
I wanna get to work
as fast as I can!
[DOCTOR 1A] Hm. Your shoulder
looks much better.
You can try swimming again,
as long as you don't overdo it.
All right?
Thanks.
[sighs]
[knocking]
Sosuke. Employee dinner.
You hungry? Dig in!
Oh, thanks a lot, Kazuma.
What you workin' so
hard on over here?
Sorry to barge in.
It's cool. I mean,
I never get very far
when I sit down to
write a letter anyway.
[KAZUMA] Yeah, I suck
at stuff like that, too.
[KAZUMA laughs]
Listen, don't worry too much
about the family.
And I can handle the
restaurant myself.
I'll be taking things over
eventually, after all.
Changing the name.
How's "Restaurant Kazuma"?
Getting ahead of
yourself, aren't ya?
Better believe it.
You have fun with that.
[BOTH laugh]
[NITORI]
Nanase's at a tournament?
Wait, you mean
that newcomer one?
[NAGISA]
Yup! Apparently, he met up with
a couple of guys he used
to do medley relays with
back in middle school,
and now they're all gonna be
on the same college
swim team together!
I think their names
are Asahi and Ikuya!
That's mostly right, except
I believe he only met up
with one of them.
[GOU]
It's a little confusing.
From what I could tell,
the team member that
Haru's already been in contact
with is named Asahi Shiina,
and the one he hasn't heard
from is named Ikuya Kirishima.
Wait, that Kirishima?
Do you know that guy, Sosuke?
[SOSUKE]
Yeah. I've seen him compete.
His style was incredibly smooth.
[REI]
At the last tournament?
You mean in the individual
medley, not the relay.
Yeah. And his freestyle...
It looked almost
exactly like Haru's.
[NAGISA]
What? You're kidding!
[REI]
I see.
Perhaps, like me, he was
enchanted by Haruka's
beautiful freestyle
and decided to adopt
that technique for himself.
If that's the case,
then maybe he's also
swimming at a Tokyo university!
If nothing else, I bet he
and Nanase'll meet again
at the newcomer
tournament today!
Okay. This is the place.
[MAKOTO]
Hey, Kisumi.
[KISUMI]
What's taking you so long?
Sorry. My train got delayed.
[KISUMI]
Hurry up!
Haru and Asahi's race
is about to start!
Yeah, I'm trying. Where are you?
[KISUMI]
I'm in the audience,
right in the middle
of the second level.
If you head upstairs,
you should see me.
Cool, be right there.
[laughs] It's been forever
since the last time
you and I raced each other.
You do remember
what I said to you
back in middle school,
don't you, Haru?
I'll catch up with you soon!
Oh, did you say that to me?
You forgot that?
C'mon, when someone
declares war,
the least you can do
is remember it!
Guess that means
we've been at war
for six years, then.
Uh-huh.
At the time, seeing
that freestyle of yours
got me so shaken up that
I couldn't even swim.
But that's not happening again.
Just made it, barely!
[KISUMI]
Yeah, that was close!
This is the first time
I've seen Asahi swim
since middle school.
Right, same here.
[KISUMI] So regardless
of who wins or loses,
everyone who beats
a certain time
goes to the All-Japan
Invitational, yeah?
[MAKOTO] No, this is
a newcomer tournament,
so no matter how good
their times are,
there's no guarantee any
of them will get selected
to move on to All-Japan.
Still. It's their first
college competition.
Which means this is a huge
debut for Haru and Asahi!
[ANNOUNCER 1A]
Take your marks.
--[beep]
--[CROWD] Go!
--Go, Asahi!
--[MAKOTO] Haru!
Look how fast they are!
That Shiina guy has got
some serious talent,
check it out.
Who knew there would be so many
impressive first-years here?
Guess I can't afford
to get lazy.
[MAKOTO]
They're picking up more speed!
[panting]
[KISUMI]
Whoa! They're way ahead!
That doesn't impress me.
Big deal. Just inferior
copies of Ikuya.
[CROWD cheers]
[ASAHI] Agh, man! I'm so
gonna own you next time.
Nah, I'll beat you again.
Oh, what makes you so confident?
You're still just
as smug as you were
in our middle school days.
[HARUKA gasps]
What's up? You okay there, Haru?
[HARUKA]
Ikuya?
[NAGISA] The gears of fate
have started to turn.
Get ready for a big reunion!
Next time: "A Promise
on a Shooting Star!"
[REI]
Wonder what thoughts
are passing through
Haruka's mind.