[NAGISA] Wow, this scenery's
amazing, huh, Romi?
[ROMIO]
Yeah, it's so cool!
[NAGISA]
Hey, look at that weird rock!
Huh? I don't see it!
[ALL yelp]
[NAGISA]
It's over there!
Oh, right!
Hah! That is pretty
weird looking!
[NAGISA] Uh-huh! This is
a lotta fun, isn't it?
Yes!
[ALL yelp]
It's just like the roller
coasters in Florida!
Hey, Coach Sasabe,
how much longer we got?
I'd say we have
about an hour left.
By the way, Ms. Amakata,
I'd be more than happy
to take over driving.
Oh, no! I'm perfectly fine!
I don't get many chances
to drive big vans like this,
so it's kind of fun!
[SASABE laughs nervously]
Hey, Ayumu. You all right?
Yes, but he seems like he
might be a little, well...
[GOU]
Rei, you're covered in sweat!
Oh, don't worry about me.
Are you sure you're okay?
Never been better.
[SASABE]
Don't try to be brave.
[GOU]
What about you, Shizu...
--[GOU] Shizuru!
--[ROMIO] Ah! Not good!
It looks like he's
accepted his fate.
[REI gags]
[ALL but AMAKATA scream, groan]
[NITORI] Welcome, swimmers,
and good morning!
I appreciate all of you
making the trip to be here.
Thanks to the relationship
built between Samezuka
and Soufuukan over spring
break, our three teams
now have the chance to enjoy
this training camp together.
If we give it our best,
I'm sure we can all learn
something new from one another.
Okay! Everybody ready?
[SWIMMERS]
Let's get started!
Oh, and one more thing--
we have a couple of
special guests joining us!
Samezuka grad, Sosuke Yamazaki!
Sosuke's here!
[NITORI] And Natsuya Kirishima,
an alumnus from Soufuukan.
I'm glad I can spend
a little time with you guys!
Kirishima...
[NITORI]
Now then!
Go ahead and get settled
into your rooms,
and we'll all meet up by
the pool at one-o'-clock!
[GOU] All three schools
are so amazing.
I'm in muscle heaven!
I have to admit,
I'm a little disappointed
there isn't a single
pudgy person here.
[MOMOTARO]
Hey, Gou!
Check out my
super-special backstroke!
I've been practicing for you!
[laughs nervously]
[laughs]
[USAMI] Didn't know you
swam backstroke, too.
Hey there, Mikoshiba.
Uh...
[USAMI] Ugh! Come on! Anago
hot spring? Table tennis?
Hey! You're the capybara!
Yep. Soufuukan High
School second year.
The King of the Rapids!
Aoba Usami.
'Kay, but I'm not gonna give up
the capybara plushie, all right?
[USAMI]
Hmph! What do you say
we have a swimming
contest this time?
You're on! Think
you can keep up?
You talk a big game.
Not for long, though.
You keep tryin',
and I'll keep winnin'.
Stay focused!
It's practice time!
[MOMOTARO]
I didn't mean right now!
[NATSUYA] If you want a contest,
just compete with me, Aoba.
[USAMI]
Natsuya?
Sorry, can't take
this one anywhere.
Ah, it's fine!
Got a bit of an attitude on him,
but he's not a bad guy.
Maybe you can all be friends.
Of course! Thank you!
[SASABE] I feel like
Nagisa's got a promising
summer ahead of him.
Me, too!
And I'd say Ryugazaki's
matured a lot
since last year as well.
That just leaves
the new blood then.
[SASABE] Shizuru's backstroke
needs some fine-tuning,
but he does have some potential.
Absolutely!
[SAMEZUKA SWIMMER 5C]
Next!
Ready!
[whistle blows]
That one's got
a hesitation problem.
He's pretty good once he
gets in the water, though.
Maybe he's just nervous today.
Ah! Hey, Romi--
[REI] Nagisa. About the training
plan for this afternoon.
[REI]
Romio?
Wonder what could
be buggin' him.
[NITORI]
That's all for today's practice!
You're welcome to train
on your own now.
Just make sure you're in the
cafeteria for dinner by six!
[SWIMMERS]
Right!
[ROMIO]
Rei, sir? Sorry.
I didn't swim enough, so I'd
like to stay behind, Captain!
That's fine with me.
Just be careful not
to overdo it, okay?
Sir!
Aw, Romi, don't leave me out!
I wanna swim, too!
[REI]
Understood.
Actually.
[REI] And, Shizuru,
why don't you come along
on a shopping run with me?
Guh-- Sure.
[NAGISA]
Okay, I reserved a lane for us.
Start at your own pace,
then try to concentrate
more on your form as you
move through the water.
Uh, right!
[sighs]
[NAGISA]
Romi?
You can go ahead and start
whenever you're ready to.
'Kay, yeah.
[CROWD cheering]
Romio!
Whoa, did you see what
just happened there?
[ANNOUNCER 5A]
In the last race...
[SOSUKE]
You're afraid to start?
Hey, Sosuke.
Is that true, Romi?
[ROMIO]
No. I mean, uh...
You're having trouble getting
the timing down, aren't you?
[gasps]
[REI] You know, Romio
seems different today.
Yeah, I noticed it, too.
You're in the same year.
Do you have any idea
what might be troubling him?
Well, uh, maybe.
[REI, GOU]
A false start?
Yeah. It was bad.
And it didn't help that
that was our last
middle school
tournament, either.
I'm guessing he's just
worried about making
the same mistake again
in high school.
And having all those
people around watching us
probably reminds him of
the day when it happened.
It was a big race.
[ROMIO]
Since then,
I've been completely
terrified of false-starting.
That's awful.
[SOSUKE]
Don't just look at the start.
Picture what comes
after you dive.
Uh?
Think about what your
reason for jumping in is.
[SOUFUUKAN SWIMMER 5A]
Looks delicious!
I know! And Iwatobi's
manager-made curry--
you should go get a plate of it.
[GOU]
Hope you enjoy!
It's a big hit!
Kunikida is a great cook!
Yup! Guess that's the
magic of secret spices!
Right, Ayumu?
[AYUMU]
Mm-hm.
And here's another batch
of the Kunikida family's
ultra-spicy curry
ready for serving!
Wow, Gou and her friend make
the greatest curry in the world!
It's almost too hot to handle.
[MOMOTARO]
Ooh, man, it burns so good!
[USAMI]
Come on, Mikoshiba.
That's what you consider spicy?
[MOMOTARO]
You're already done?
Huh. Yeah, and I'm
on my way to get
a heaping plate of seconds.
Ready for more, Gou!
Hey, what's your deal?
You're not worthy of
Gou's amazing curry!
What? I've had it with you!
[NAGISA]
Mm! This is really yummy!
[GOU giggles] Ayumu gets
all the credit for that.
[REI]
It's magnificent!
[AYUMU] Thanks, it's an
old family recipe.
Huh? Seaweed?
But... Why would you...?
Because it tastes
better with seaweed.
[ROMIO]
If you say so.
That looks great!
There's plenty more
if you want some.
Did you bring that along
from home, Shizuru?
[SHIZURU] Yeah. My family
runs a seafood store.
[ROMIO] They gather their
inventory by skin-diving.
That's how Shizuru became
such a talented swimmer.
Ah, that's interesting.
Uh-huh!
So, did you get to
eat a lot of curry
when you lived in New York?
Yeah!
[GOU]
I hear it's different there!
At this one place,
they're famous
for serving up the
world's spiciest recipe!
[GOU]
Oh, wow! No kidding?
[AYUMU] How spicy is it?
Please, tell me everything!
[ROMIO] It's so intense,
the chef wears a gas mask
while he's preparing it!
[GOU]
No way!
[ROMIO] It's true! I went
with my family one time!
[NITORI]
So, for the last day of camp,
I thought having a time trial
for each of the four strokes
might be a good idea.
Works for me.
I dunno, it is the last day--
shouldn't we do
something special?
[NITORI]
Any thoughts, guys?
But of course.
Actually, if you don't mind,
we have a proposition.
[SWIM COACH 5A]
Let's say hello to our new
swimming coach, everybody.
Nice to meet all of you.
I'm Coach Tachibana.
[applause]
People you swim with
all seem to end up
suffering, don't they?
[sighs]
[RIN]
What about you, though?
Don't you wanna get
to that point yourself?
[NATSUYA]
Hey. Great day, huh?
[NATSUYA] Haven't seen you
since the hot spring.
Yeah.
Listen, correct me if I'm wrong,
but do you have a
brother named Ikuya?
Whoa, no way!
So you guys know
each other then?
Uh, well, no.
It's just, I saw him swim
at nationals in high school.
Gotcha.
Yup. That was my little
brother, all right.
There was something remarkable
about the way he swam.
Uh-huh! Can ya tell
how proud I am?
[SOSUKE] So, uh, what,
keeps you busy Kirishima?
[NATSUYA] Oh, y'know,
swimming wherever I want,
whenever I want.
Travelling the world,
entering races.
You meet a lot of
cool people that way.
Like, I was just in Australia,
and I met this Japanese
guy who's been preparing
for the global stage ever
since he was a little kid.
I liked how solid and
straightforward he was.
And obviously super
passionate about the sport.
[chuckles]
What's so funny?
Sorry. That reminds me
of somebody I know.
Oh, yeah?
That's weird--one time
while we were talking
he told me that I reminded
him of someone he knows.
A guy he wants to swim
with again someday.
Really? What a coincidence.
So, uh...
I heard you suffered
a shoulder injury.
How's it healin' up?
Not too bad.
The doctor says if I
keep up with my rehab,
I should be able to swim again.
I probably won't
be strong enough
to compete anymore, though.
But, if I have surgery...
Then you could go
back to competitions,
unless the treatment
didn't work out,
which would ruin your
swimming career for good.
Is that right?
That's a tough
choice for anyone.
[NATSUYA]
Sosuke Yamazaki.
I didn't put it together
right away when I heard
you graduated from Samezuka.
But you went to
Tokitsu High, too.
You were famous
for your butterfly
back in those days, weren't you?
Yeah, until I hurt my shoulder.
But if it healed up,
you'd be good enough
to compete internationally.
[NATSUYA] Allow me to share
a few words of wisdom
that I think'll
do you some good.
They're from Mikhail,
the greatest coach
to ever come out of the
Russian swimming world.
He once said, "Victory
only comes to people
who believe in themselves."
Inspiring, huh? Those
words really struck me.
What I heard was, "win or lose,
life is what you make of it."
Next thing I knew,
I was on a plane.
[NATSUYA]
Now that quote's my mantra.
[gasps]
[REI]
Well, this is it, team.
Tomorrow is the final day
of our training camp.
And for the grand finale,
we've decided to hold
a medley relay between all
three schools in attendance!
That sounds awesome!
Um, the first-year guys, too?
[REI]
Naturally!
Uh--
Shizu's backstroke and
Romi's swimming freestyle!
That's the first leg.
But it's way too soon!
And you want me
to be the anchor?
I assure you, such apprehension
is entirely unwarranted.
We'll be right there
to support you.
We're just practicing.
So we can have some fun with it!
[ROMIO]
But...
Sorry. I just can't.
It would be my first
relay, and, besides...
Starting...
[GOU]
Romio.
It's all right. Don't try
to carry this burden alone.
We're here to help you
overcome your fear.
This is a team, after all!
Being a team means all of us
are swimming toward one goal.
That's right.
Your teammates have
got your back.
So lean on us! And just
dive in with all you've got!
Okay?
[ROMIO]
Teammates...
[SAMEZUKA SWIMMER 5C]
Remember to keep that energy up!
[SWIMMERS]
Right!
It's just practice,
but I'm here to win!
Rei and Nagisa really put
some planning into this, huh?
Yes.
A relay competition.
Now that's not a bad idea.
The suggestion came
from Iwatobi High.
They wanna grow as a team.
Makes sense.
[REI] This brings back
memories of the very first
relay we swam with
Makoto and Haruka.
I know, right?
And we weren't really prepared
for it back then, either.
True.
Actually, that was my first time
participating in a relay, too.
Perhaps all I managed
to do in that race
was hold the rest
of the team back.
But still, the burning
emotion I felt when we all
swam together as a team
still lives on to this day.
Deep in my heart.
And now, it's the source
of all my confidence.
Yup!
So I say we get ready to
have as much fun as we can
in this relay,
Iwatobi Swim Club style!
[REI, SHIZURU, ROMIO]
Okay!
Well, the water's waiting!
There's still time to
back out if you're chicken.
Yeah, in your
dreams, scaredy-cat!
[SAMEZUKA SWIMMER 5C]
Take your marks.
--[whistle blows]
--[SWIMMERS] Go!
All right! Go, Shizu!
[SAMEZUKA SWIMMER 5A]
Momo's in the lead!
[SAMEZUKA SWIMMER 5B]
Lookin' good, Momotaro!
[SOUFUUKAN SWIMMER 5A]
You can do it, Aoba!
[AMAKATA]
You got this, Isurugi!
[GOU]
Let's go!
Iwatobi's smoking 'em!
[GOU]
You're doing great, Nagisa!
[SASABE] Yeah, Nagisa,
that's how it's done!
[REI] Romio.
I promise, whatever happens,
I'll hand you a good
position in the relay.
So just dive in
with all your heart.
Go, Rei!
Awesome exchange.
[ROMIO]
Mm.
[SOSUKE] Picture what
comes after you dive.
[ROMIO]
After I dive.
[REI]
Being a team means all of us
are swimming toward one goal.
[ROMIO]
All of us.
[REI]
I promise, whatever happens,
I'll hand you a good
position in the relay.
Your teammates
have got your back.
So lean on us!
[SAMEZUKA SWIMMER 5D]
Whoa, it's close!
Think about what your
reason for jumping in is.
[ROMIO]
Right now...
[REI] It's the source
of all my confidence.
[ROMIO]
This is it!
Not yet.
That was perfect!
--[NAGISA] Great job!
--[SHIZURU] Romi!
Yeah!
A clean start!
Ha, we showed you!
And that's the
power of Samezuka!
[USAMI]
Hmph. You got lucky this time.
[MINAMI]
That was a good race.
[NITORI]
Yeah, I agree!
You did it, Romi!
Whoa, Nagisa!
You dove so well.
Yes, it was exquisite!
[ROMIO]
But, guys, we lost.
So? That exchange
was incredible!
Right!
[SHIZURU]
I'm... so proud of you.
[ROMIO]
Hey! Um.
Okay, you don't have
to cry about it!
[laughs] You're a
sensitive guy, huh?
[REI]
Shizuru, you were great as well!
I knew you could.
I got the same feeling
out there you did, Captain.
And because of that.
Now I'm even more frustrated!
We have to win the next one!
Well, we just need
to work a lot harder!
Indeed. All four of us.
Because we are a team!
[ROMIO, SHIZURU]
Yeah!
[NATSUYA]
Yamazaki.
Have you made your mind up yet?
Not yet. I, uh...
[NATSUYA] Hey. What do ya
say we make a little bet?
A bet?
[NATSUYA] If you can pick
which hand I'm hiding
the coin in, then
you keep believing
in your dream and move
forward. No excuses.
Okay. And if I pick
the other hand?
[NATSUYA] If you choose that
one, you have to take a break.
Sometimes in life,
you gotta take the long road.
Relax, loosen up a little.
Here goes.
Pick one.
[SOSUKE]
The right.
Final answer?
On second thought, never mind.
I'd rather decide for myself.
Good plan.
Okay.
Take care. It's been fun.
[SOSUKE]
Yeah.
Yeah. I think he's gonna
turn out all right.
[MISAKI]
Check it out, Coach!
[MAKOTO]
Huh? What is it?
Look!
That's our old coach
who moved away before!
[gasps] That's Nao!
[NAGISA] The past. Events
that cannot be changed.
[REI] The future: a vision that
gives us hope and expectation!
[NAGISA] Next time:
"Mermaid of the Abyss!"