[phone buzzes]
Hey.
[MAKOTO] Hi, Haru?
Do you have a minute?
Yeah, what's up?
[MAKOTO] You know how
we bought suits for the
University Entrance
Ceremony yesterday?
Well, it looks like they
gave me the voucher
for your suit on accident.
So yeah, I was wondering
if you might have mine.
I've got it.
[MAKOTO] Really? Okay good.
That's a relief.
I couldn't find it anywhere,
so I was starting to worry
that I might've dropped it.
Wanna meet up later today
and grab our suits together?
[MAKOTO]
Good thinkin'.
Yeah. Would you be
free to meet up at six?
I've got a few places I
need to stop by beforehand.
Don't tell me you're
still trying to hunt down
those presents for Ren and Ran.
[MAKOTO] I am. Apparently
they're super popular.
None of the stores I've been to
had any in stock. But still...
...sounds like the twins have
wanted these for a long time,
so I'm gonna try and track some
down before their birthday.
Okay. Well, hopefully you'll
be able to find them.
Thanks, I appreciate it.
Anyway, I'll see you
at the store at six.
Right. I'll be in touch later.
I'd better go soon. I've got
my keys and wallet on me...
Wait. Where's... Where's my bag?
[OMASA] I think we drove
past here in the truck,
but I'm not sure.
Aw, I don't see it anywhere.
[YAMANAKA groans] Crap!
This event is a do-or-die,
once-in-a-lifetime
chance for Iwatobi!
But we lost the
beak in transport.
And Fujii was supposed
to wear the costume,
but now he's running late!
He says he won't be able
to make it until four PM.
[yells] That isn't even
close to soon enough--
the first match'll be over!
You wear it in
his place, Kasahara!
I would, but I have a crippling
fear of mascot costumes.
Well then why did
you take this job?
We do nothing but
follow a mascot around!
Won't you be fine once
you're inside the thing?
Too scary.
[YAMANAKA groans] I'd do it
myself if not for my hernia.
[yelps]
It's all over. Little Iwatobi's
gonna lose by default.
Don't even talk like that,
we're not gonna let that happen!
Our mission is to make
Little Iwatobi's name famous!
To help all of Japan to
recognize the greatness
of the town of Iwatobi!
[gasps] Wow, Yamanaka.
Our Little Iwatobi's
about to dive to the future.
Yeah? Then I sure
hope you have a plan.
Indeed I do. Before the first
match of the tournament,
we're gonna find
ourselves a beak,
and a substitute wrestler!
[KASAHARA, OMASA]
Hm! Yes, sir!
[HARUKA]
Hm?
[HARUKA] This looks like...
Little Iwatobi's beak.
But why is it here?
[MAKOTO groans] They're sold
out everywhere. Oh well.
Where do I go to next? Uh...
[MAKOTO]
"Regional Mascot Sumo"?
[MAKOTO chuckles]
Bet Haru would love that.
[REI] I'm roughly ten
meters from the target.
According to my best estimate,
I should be working with
a zero point five meter
per second tailwind, with a
moderate drift to the left.
So if my calculations
are correct...
...with this much force...
...coming from this angle...
...I'll hit dead on!
Huh? The wind
suddenly shifted.
[whistle blows]
Why?!
Aw, man. That wasn't even close.
[MOMOTARO]
Yeah!
[REI]
I'm sorry.
No worries.
I think you go next, Momo.
Okay! Here goes!
Behold my Ultra
Stream Otter Kick!
[NITORI]
What?! Two panels!
Momo's crazy, but he's
still a real threat...
[REI] No way.
He had such sloppy form.
[NITORI grunts]
[NAGISA grunts]
[NAGISA, UOZUMI, MOMOTARO]
All right!
[MOMOTARO]
A fabulous prize, woo hoo!
[NAGISA]
Hey, Rei. Ya want some?
[NAGISA chuckles]
I'd love some,
thank you, Nagisa.
[NITORI] Does Iwatobi throw a
festival like this every year?
[REI]
No. This is the first one.
The chamber of commerce started
it to try to liven up the town.
It seems to be going
pretty well. I like it.
Yeah. I'm glad we got a chance
to relax, after a whole
spring break of
"Mikoshiba's special training."
Heh. It feels as though
providence brought us
to this festival to
reward our hard work.
A little surprise gift from
the spring breeze itself.
Yeah. Sure.
I doubt I would've come here
if you hadn't invited me,
so thanks, Nagisa.
Of course, festivals are always
more fun with lots of people.
[MOMOTARO]
Not that you guys aren't fun,
but I wish Gou could've
made it out, too.
She's with her family right now,
but she said she'd come later.
Yahoo!
Oh! Say, does anyone else
feel like getting lunch soon?
Yes, I could eat.
All the snacks I had just made
me hungrier for some real food.
[gasps] Hey! Here's an idea!
Let's grab some food and
then eat over there!
Iwatobi's doing a sumo match?
[REI] Yeah, they're having
a mascot tournament in Tokyo,
and the whole thing'll
be streamed online.
[UOZUMI]
What even is a Little Iwatobi?
[NAGISA]
H-Huh?! Oh, come on!
Iwa means "boulder,"
tobi means "black kite,"
so it's a boulder-headed bird!
You might also want to mention
that it's the regional mascot.
Yeah, I've seen it before.
Gotta say, a bird with a rock
for a head is pretty weird.
[NAGISA] Give it a rest,
it's not that weird!
Just look at the screen.
Little Iwatobi's adorable!
And he'll be even
cuter in motion,
so let's cheer him on together!
[footsteps]
[MIYAKO]
Oh.
It figures Rin would've
stopped by before he left.
'Course he would.
[GOU] Hey, Dad. I'm guessing
Rin told you this himself.
But he's leaving home to do
some training in Australia,
so please watch over
him while he's away.
And please watch over
me and Mom, too.
We'll be counting on you.
[chuckles] You've given
him quite the workload.
That's cause I know
Dad can handle it!
Anyway, I gotta go.
The festival's already
gotten started.
Why the rush? Got a date?
[gasps] No way.
I'm just going to meet up
with Hana and a few other
friends, that's all.
Oh. All right, I'll let you
leave it at that for now.
'Kay, I'd better get going.
I'll call you when
I'm on my way home.
Sure. You make good
choices, all right?
Rin and Gou are both
doing great, dear.
We love you.
[RIN] It's finally time
to take on the world.
[RIN] Hey, old man.
You're watchin' right?
'Cause I'm just gettin' started.
[ASAHI]
'Sup, Kisumi?
Yo!
So, I kinda got lost
on the way over here.
Hey, at least you made it.
Heck yeah. How've ya been?
I see you're already
getting a head start
in the working man department,
what's that like?
Oh, well, my uncle's in real
estate and this is his office.
I've been working here
since spring break started.
It's a good gig.
That would explain why
you weren't in Iwatobi!
It was my first time back
in ages. I missed you, man.
I heard you brought a whole
bunch of millet dumplings
for my family.
Hayato was super excited.
Oh, yeah. Your brother's
growing up crazy fast.
Threw me for a loop.
Anyway, I brought a few
things for you, too.
[KISUMI]
Oh, cool, thanks!
I gotta admit, you're
unexpectedly considerate
when it comes to
this kinda thing.
Why would that be unexpected?
Do ya wanna stick around
and have some tea?
I would If I could, but I
need to run and pick up
my suit for the
entrance ceremony.
Gotta do what'cha gotta do.
[ASAHI] Hm. At least we're
goin' to the same college,
am I right? I'll catch
you at the ceremony.
Right, I'll see ya
pretty soon then.
So you got in with a
sports recommendation?
[ASAHI]
Yeah.
Well, now I can't
wait for college.
I'll get to play
basketball with ya.
[ASAHI] I got in for swimming,
you know that, dude!
[KISUMI] Ha! Yeah. Hey, before
you take off, one thing.
The other day,
Makoto and Haru came--
--[phone buzzing]
--[ASAHI] Ah. One second.
Shoot. It's from my sister.
I'm s'posed to grab a few
things for her. I'd better go.
Thanks for the present.
You're good.
No prob, Kisumi.
I'll see ya. Take care.
Sure thing.
Well. It's fine, I'll have lots
of chances to tell him later.
[MAKOTO groans] Can't seem
to find them anywhere.
Sorry! I didn't see you.
Little Iwatobi?
Wait!
Sir. I take it you know
who Little Iwatobi is?
Uh. Yeah. I mean I'm from
Iwatobi, so there's that.
Oh, yeah, he's the one.
Agreed. He's athletic,
and the right height.
What now?
You don't have a crippling
fear of mascot costumes,
--now do ya?
--[MAKOTO] Huh?
[OMASA] You like Iwatobi, right?
You're a fan, aren't you?
Yeah. Sure.
Then it seems to me that
this is your lucky day,
and ours as well.
[MAKOTO chuckles]
Kay.
[GROUP] Please, sir: the town
of Iwatobi is in your hands!
[MAKOTO]
I would, but I'm--
[YAMANAKA] But, I'm sure you
can be a little late, right?
C'mon, just hear us out, we'll
treat you well, I promise.
Huh.
Tokyo really is
bustling, isn't it?
[IKUYA]
Yeah, makes it hard to relax.
Aw...
Personally, I've been looking
forward to moving out here.
It's a definite change
of pace from Kyoto.
But there're still
some quiet places.
This café has a nice vibe.
I don't exactly hate it.
Ha! I figured you would
say something like that.
Oh, yeah, Have you gotten a suit
for the entrance ceremony?
Haven't had a chance.
[HIYORI] What? You know it's
the day after tomorrow, right?
[phone buzzes]
[HIYORI]
What's up?
It's from Natsuya.
He texted "don't overdo it."
He doesn't know what
he's talking about.
[laughs] It sounds like he's
just worried about you.
That's what big
brothers are for.
But I'm not a kid anymore.
[HIYORI] Well, as your
friend, I'm worried, too.
If you've suddenly become
such a responsible adult,
then where's your suit
for the entrance ceremony?
I know! Why don't we
shop for one together?
[IKUYA]
I'm still eating.
[NATSUYA]
Hey. Nao. How've you been?
Not bad. It's good to hear ya.
How are the States treating you?
[NATSUYA]
All right.
Just finished a race
in San Francisco.
And right now, I'm about
to get on a bus to LA.
[NAO]
Sounds like an intense schedule.
Well, I'm used to it. What's new
on your end? Ya done moving yet?
[NAO]
Finished last week.
It sucked havin' to move from
my old place just 'cause
the campus changed
locations, but that's life.
[NATSUYA] So did you
have to quit your job
at the district pool then?
Yeah. I'm really gonna
miss my students.
Didn't get to tell
them all bye either,
so that was disappointing.
Too bad, but I bet a lot of
them'll keep on swimming,
and, as long as they do,
you never know...
You might run into
them again someday.
Yeah. I hope that happens.
Oh, and speaking of which.
Your brother'll be at a college
in Tokyo come April, right?
Scary stuff. You okay?
Don't talk to me like I'm
an overprotective parent.
[NATSUYA]
Turns out,
Ikuya's friend Hiyori is going
to Shimogami with him.
So he won't be alone.
[NAO]
Yeah, he'll be fine.
[NATSUYA] Anyway. I'll bring
a little somethin' back for ya
the next time I'm in Japan.
[NAO laughs]
Looking forward to it.
I've got those weird dolls you
brought me last time sitting in
a place of honor on my desk.
Oh. I think those were
tournament mascots.
Had no idea what
they were at the time.
They're great.
I'm excited to see what
souvenir ya get me next.
Hey, a gag gift's better than
no gift, so drop the tone.
Heh. Well, what do I care?
Till next time, Nao.
[NAO]
Yeah. Catch you later, Natsuya.
[GOU]
Sosuke, over here!
[GOU laughs]
Hey, I'm glad you made it!
--[HANAMURA] Good afternoon.
--[SOSUKE] Hey.
It was nice of you to come
and hang out with us today.
Will things be okay at the
restaurant without you?
Yeah. My cousin who's
the chef is helping today,
so I got the day off.
Sosuke helps out at the
restaurant his family owns.
Wow, that's pretty cool.
So do you plan to take
over the family business?
--No. I, uh...
--[NAGISA] Gou! Sosuke! Hana!
There you are!
What's up, Nag? We're
not too late, are we?
Nah! Everyone's gathered
over there, come on!
Sosuke, what's up?
I'm glad you could make it out!
[BOYS]
Same here!
[SOSUKE]
Thanks.
We got permission
to slack off today!
Tell ya what, Gou: how about I
get us both some yakisoba ?
[GOU] Thanks, but I
already had lunch, so...
What's goin' on here,
some kinda show?
They're livestreaming
Little Iwatobi
as he competes in a regional
mascot sumo tournament.
So all of us decided to watch it
from here as a show of support.
Isn't Little Iwatobi the
mascot Haru likes?
You guessed it!
That's our Sosuke!
Unless I'm mistaken, the match
should start any second.
[MAKOTO] Wait, so... You want
me to dress up as Iwatobi
and battle another mascot?
Look, it's not a pit fight,
it's a sumo match.
It'll all be very civilized.
I realize this is sudden,
but your hometown needs you,
so please rise up
to the challenge!
[OMASA] I'm done taking
his measurements!
The staffer who was meant
to do this is on his way.
He should be here
by the next match.
[MAKOTO] Wait. Sorry, but uh...
Shouldn't this guy have a beak?
--[BOTH gasps]
--[MAKOTO] Hm?
Yeah, he should have a beak.
But we lost it in transit.
[MAKOTO]
Huh?
[OMASA sobs]
[YAMANAKA] Even now. Our people
are doing their best to find it.
Guess fake beaks are
hard to come by.
[YAMANAKA]
We need your help!
[OMASA] Please, sir!
Just be the sub for one match!
We won't keep you here
for any longer, we promise!
[YAMANAKA]
It's just one match!
All right, I'll do it.
I still have a little more time
before I'm supposed to meet
my friend, so if
I'm who you want...
[BOTH gasp]
[MIKOSHIBA] Hey! This
sure is a coincidence.
I wasn't expecting to
run into you here.
Same. Are you
out shopping, or...?
[MIKOSHIBA] Yeah. Momotaro's
been pestering me for a toy.
Somethin' to do with 3D deep
sea creatures. It's funny.
He's in high school now,
but he still has the taste
of a grade-schooler.
Think I remember seeing
that toy somewhere in there.
[MIKOSHIBA] Oh cool. Really?
Well, that works out.
I guess this shop is one of
those well-kept secrets, huh?
Uh... What'cha got there?
I'm pretty sure it's
Little Iwatobi's beak.
I found it on the
side of the road.
How'd somethin' like
that end up in Tokyo?
Wait, now that I think about it,
I saw there's some kind of
regional mascot
thing goin' on today.
Yeah! Tachibana was
involved somehow!
Where'd you see him?
[YAMANAKA] How's it feel?
Everything tight?
[MAKOTO]
Uh yeah! Real tight.
[YAMANAKA] I'm extremely
reluctant to present
Little Iwatobi to the world
in this improvised state.
But I think we've done
all we can for now.
[MAKOTO]
Right.
[MAKOTO sighs] I cannot
let Haru see me like this.
--[HARUKA] Is Iwatobi here?
--[MAKOTO gasps]
[HARUKA gasps]
S'cuse me.
[YAMANAKA gasps]
Y-You found it!
[KASAHARA]
Iwatobi's beak!
[OMASA] This is amazing,
thanks for bringing it!
[YAMANAKA] What a relief.
Now we can show our
Little Iwatobi to the country
with full confidence!
We're in your debt, truly!
[HARUKA]
Sure.
[YAMANAKA]
All right, Iwatobi.
[MAKOTO gasps]
[YAMANAKA] Turn around so I
can switch out your beak--
Hey, why are you running?
I'm not gonna hurt you!
[YAMANAKA]
Mr. Tachibana, please!
I can't let you do the
match with the wrong beak!
--Come back!
--[HARUKA] Hey, Makoto.
[MAKOTO]
Hi.
[YAMANAKA] Oh. So the two
of you know each other.
That explains
everything, actually.
Let's all do our best
as a team, okay?
So how--
[MAKOTO]
Please don't ask right now.
[NAGISA] Check it out!
The match is starting!
[NITORI] I'm starting to feel
the hype all of a sudden.
[UOZUMI] Huh, that looks like
a pretty professional set-up.
[MIRACLE GLOVES-KUN grunts]
[gasps]
[REFEREE A]
Contestants,
please take your
starting positions!
[MAKOTO] I have to give my all.
This is for Iwatobi.
For my home!
You can do this.
[REFEREE A]
Ready... Fight!
[OMASA gasps]
Get in there! Fight him!
[MIRACLE GLOVES-KUN shouts]
[MIRACLE GLOVES-KUN]
Come and get it. Rockhead.
Damn it! It's not a rock,
it's a boulder!
[BOTH grunting]
He's strong. Can't move.
Fight back! Kick his butt!
Do your best, okay?
[REI gasps]
Hey, is something the matter?
[GOU] Not really, it's just
the muscles on those legs
look strangely familiar.
Hey, uh... That's Haru.
[NAGISA] Right? There,
in the background?
[REI] I think you're right!
That's Haruka for sure!
Oh, and... It's hard
tell at this distance,
but I think I see
Makoto's backpack.
[NAGISA]
Yeah, I see it, too!
That's whose legs they are!
I'm certain now.
I'd know those calves anywhere!
Makoto's gotta be in there!
Whoa!
It's Makoto's on that stage!
He's fighting for the
pride of Iwatobi!
[grunting]
I can't get a grip on him.
Hang in there!
[MAKOTO]
It's no use. I'm gonna lose.
Hey, Makato! Use a backstroke!
--[gasps]
--Your backstroke! Use it!
[MAKOTO] My backstroke?
What does he mean?
[MIRACLE GLOVES-KUN]
Huh? What the...?
He stopped the assault!
It's Mako's famous backstroke!
[grunts]
[MIRACLE GLOVES-KUN gasps]
[BOTH]
I've seen that move!
It's a Makoto specialty!
His off-the-wall push!
[ALL gasp]
[MAKOTO grunts]
The winner is Little Iwatobi!
[MAKOTO]
Hey! A-Are you all right?
[MIRACLE GLOVES-KUN]
Well done.
You'll be a great
mascot someday!
[MAKOTO]
Thanks, I mean, I think.
Are ya startin' to wish that
it was you in that spotlight?
I'm not.
[NAGISA]
Way to go!
Makoto came through for us!
I knew he could pull it off.
[UOZUMI]
Man. He really put on a show.
[MINAMI]
He sure did.
[MAKOTO]
Talk about a crazy day.
I wonder if that was what
Miss A meant by the
"baptism of Tokyo."
I feel like this had more to do
with Iwatobi than Tokyo though.
[phone buzzes]
Oh. It's Nagisa.
[NAGISA] Hey, Mako! I saw
your Little Iwatobi match!
Say what? You've gotta
be kidding, how?
[REI] They live-streamed the
entire match at the festival.
All of us watched it together.
[GOU] Nice fight, Makoto!
You were awesome!
[MAKOTO gasps]
[MOMOTARO] Yeah, what she said!
That was super cool!
[SOSUKE]
Backstroke for days.
Wait. Sosuke watched it?
Do your best in the
next match, too!
[MAKOTO] I was just a sub,
so I won't be in the next match.
Aw, that's disappointing.
Anyway, tell Haru
we all said hi.
[MAKOTO] Will do. Tell everyone
that we said hi, too.
Sure! Buh-bye!
See ya... Ugh...
Oh, yeah. Makoto. Look here.
Huh? The twin organisms Namako
and Senjunamako! No way!
Can't believe you
remembered that.
Well, I've only been
looking for them forever.
Here they are.
Huh? Did you get them for me?
Yeah. You said Ren and
Ran wanted them, right?
[MAKOTO]
Mm-hm! This means a lot, Haru.
[HARUKA]
Should we go get our suits?
[MAKOTO]
Sure.
[laughs]
[HIYORI] It's a waste, ya know.
You looked great in that suit.
For real. That was the
one for you, I mean it.
I wanna choose these
things for myself.
[HIYORI]
Do ya have to be stubborn?
Oh, well, that is one of the
things I like about you.
[IKUYA]
What's that mean?
[MAKOTO]
Feel like I'm playing dress-up.
It's embarrassing.
I think we've found your suit.
You look so handsome.
Thanks, you really think so?
[curtain clatters]
Wow! You boys make
a dashing pair.
It's so stuffy.
[MAKOTO chuckles]
Haru.
I don't know about you,
but I'm starting to
feel like an adult now.
Same here.
[MAKOTO] Even then, I think
we were still just kids,
but the curtain was about to
rise on our college lives.
It's quite the story,
but it's for another time.
[NAGISA] Haru and the
others are finally starting
their new lives!
[REI]
Exciting stuff, we know.
[NAGISA] Next time:
"Sprouting Dive Start!"
[REI]
Look forward to it!