[IKUYA] Once upon a time,
nestled far, far below
the land where
human beings lived...
[IKUYA]
At the bottom of the ocean,
which flowed so clear,
like purest glass--
there was the mermaid's kingdom.
[ASAHI]
See?
Kisumi told us Shimogami
doesn't have practice today.
[HARUKA]
Wow, he was actually right.
Jeez, have a little
faith in your friend!
[laughs] It's early in the day,
so he might still be in class.
Do you know what
department he's in?
[ASAHI]
Agh, dammit. I forgot to ask!
Asahi.
What's up? Did you see Ikuya?
Not yet.
We need to find out
what department
his classes are in first.
[KISUMI]
Sorry, I don't have that info.
Ugh. Are you kidding?
I thought you said
you made friends
with an upperclassman who's
dating one of their guys!
Just ask her!
I would, but I don't
think I can reach her.
I'm pretty sure she had made
plans to go to a movie
with her boyfriend today. Sorry!
They're going to see
A Rat's Life 2 , actually.
That sounds terrible.
[MAKOTO] I guess we'll just have
to check all the departments
and hope we get lucky.
We won't find him by
wandering around.
Uh--
What the...? You again?!
[ASAHI]
Hello, Archerfish!
I told you not to call me that!
Hey, quiet down.
Listen, Archerfish.
[growls]
Ikuya Kirishima.
We're here to see him.
[TERASHIMA] Ha! Sorry,
there's no practice today.
In fact, I was just
on my way to the movies
with my girlfriend.
We scored some tickets
to A Rat's Life 2 !
Wait a minute.
Uh-- Oh, come on.
There is no way Kisumi's
friend's boyfriend
and this jerk are
the same person.
What's the matter?
Do you guys know Misae,
too, or something?
Hang on, let me make sure.
[ASAHI]
Mm. It's a match.
I can't believe my own
girlfriend calls me Archerfish!
There's no justice
in this world!
Anyway.
Am I boring you?
Do you know where we
can find Ikuya right now?
Gimme one good reason
why I should help you guys.
I'd play nice if I were you.
We can tell our friend to
talk to your girl and say.
"Terashima's so awesome!"
If you give us some
intel on Ikuya.
Hey, you okay?
[HIYORI] Yeah, just remembered
I need to do something.
Why don't you go on to
the pool without me, 'kay?
[IKUYA]
'Kay.
Well, good luck with
whatever you're doin'.
Thanks. I won't be too long.
Empty.
Maybe they left for the day.
[HIYORI]
What are you three doin' here?
We came here to
visit our friend.
You got some kinda
problem with that?
Oh, this again?
Ikuya's too busy
to waste his time
reminiscing on childish things.
--Screw you!
--[HARUKA] Calm down.
Nanase, wasn't it?
I thought I was clear
when we talked before.
Ikuya has a very full schedule.
But there's no practice today.
[HIYORI] No, that's why he's
practicing solo instead.
I'd rather you not disturb him.
We won't interrupt
his training, okay?
We only wanna talk to him
for a few minutes.
[sighs]
Well, I can see you're
not backing down,
but at least wait
until he's finished?
He should be done in
about two hours or so.
[ASAHI] Ugh! I get a bad
feeling from that guy.
It's no big deal.
The important thing is that
we get to visit Ikuya.
So, what do you think
we should say to him?
[MAKOTO] Hm. Well, first,
we'd better apologize.
And then, uh...
[ASAHI]
Go on.
I wanna talk to him about
the summer training camp
we all did in middle school.
Oh, yeah, I forgot
all about that!
But you were the one
who suggested it.
That night while you
guys were asleep,
Ikuya and I had a talk.
[HARUKA] He asked if I'd
race him in freestyle
the next summer.
And then, he made a wish
on a shooting star.
You never told us about that.
Yeah, I wonder what
Ikuya was wishing for.
[HIGASHI]
A pork cutlet bowl.
Say wha...?
That's what I wish I had,
but the ones at this
place are no good.
They have good mackerel.
There's no such thing
as good mackerel.
So, we meet again, fellas.
[MAKOTO]
It's that guy.
Yeah, what a coincidence.
Word to the wise, boys.
Always order the
kitsune udon here.
It's the best.
Okay...?
Enjoy your day.
Who is that?
Something tells me he's
not a student here.
[IKUYA] Damn it!
I thought I got over this!
[IKUYA gasps]
[IKUYA]
Not again.
I guess... I'm just...
[SHIMOGAMI SWIMMER 4A]
Hey, Kirishima!
[SHIMOGAMI SWIMMER 4B]
He sank!
Ikuya!
[panting]
[HIYORI]
Hey! You all right?
Yeah, I'm fine.
Leave me alone, okay?
[gasps]
[MAKOTO] We're kinda early,
don't you think?
[ASAHI]
Beats being too late.
Maybe this way we can
avoid Ikuya's bodyguard.
Not here.
Come on! He lied
to us, didn't he?
[HIYORI] Now that's rude.
Of course I wasn't lying to you.
[HARUKA]
We waited, just like you said.
Now let us see him.
[HIYORI]
He already left.
He wasn't feeling very well,
so he decided to finish
practicing early and
turn in for the evening.
Did he now?
Why would I lie about
something like that?
If that's the case,
then we'll just go
check in on him.
You don't mind putting us
in touch with him, do you?
Maybe you should
forget about Ikuya
and mind your own business.
Sorry, but if something's
going on with our friend,
that is our business!
[HIYORI] Like I said,
this is an especially
crucial time for him.
You're athletes, too.
You should understand.
We do understand, but you
better cut the attitude!
Let it go, Asahi.
Sorry. I didn't
mean it that way.
So, you guys friends, or what?
I'm his best friend.
I guess I haven't
introduced myself, have I?
My name's Hiyori Toono.
Ikuya and I got
to know each other
while we were studying
abroad in America.
When we came back to Japan,
his older brother,
Natsuya, asked me
to look after him.
Then that means you
know about us already.
[HIYORI] Oh, he might have
mentioned you once or twice.
If I remember correctly,
you were his teammates,
but you broke up the Swim Club
before your second
year of middle school.
That's why we're here.
We've been trying
to apologize to him.
[HIYORI] What good do you
think that'll do now?
During our first summer
break in middle school,
I made him a promise.
I told him I'd race him in
freestyle the summer after.
I just wanna make sure
he knows how sorry I am
that I didn't make
good on my word.
How noble, but that
was so long ago.
He probably doesn't
even remember it now.
You're just being a nuisance.
Oh, and by the way, guys,
Ikuya doesn't swim
relays anymore.
He decided to switch his
focus to the IM a while back.
You know somethin'?
I'm gettin' sick of hearin'
you speak for Ikuya
like you're his damn boss.
[HIYORI] His brother
asked me to protect him.
We've known Natsuya
even longer than you have!
We've been friends with Ikuya
since middle school, remember?
But I'm his best friend.
Middle school is one thing,
but if we're talking about
being friends with Ikuya now,
you three don't have the right.
"The right"? The hell we don't!
[HIYORI] He's well on his
way to the global stage.
Weaklings like you
would drag him down.
If you're not strong,
you simply don't deserve
to be around him.
That's what I think.
--[ASAHI] Oh, yeah?
--Let's settle this with a race.
Haru!
Hah! Race? Great idea.
We'll compete with the
right to be friends
with Ikuya on the line.
Oh, but wait,
my specialty's backstroke.
And you only swim free.
If I know one thing
about you, it's that.
That's fine, though.
I'm happy to swim
freestyle instead.
So then. Shall we race?
[MAKOTO] I'll race you.
Let's do backstroke.
Makoto.
It's gonna be okay, Haru.
Trust me.
[gasps]
Tachibana. That right?
Ah, so you're going to
step up and race me instead?
That sounds like a plan.
This ought to be interesting.
We'll see just how
serious you are.
[ASAHI] Are you sure you're
okay with doing this, Makoto?
[MAKOTO]
Mm-hm. It kinda gave me the urge
to swim for real again.
Besides, our friendship with
Ikuya's worth fighting for.
[AKANE]
What's all this?
You're having a race against
one of Ikuya's friends?
Do you mind if I come
to cheer you guys on?
This isn't exactly
a happy occasion, sis.
It'd be really weird
to have an audience.
Okay, then.
[KISUMI] Makoto! I just
heard about your race!
Can I come?
No! Like I just said,
it's not that kinda race!
Come on, Asahi, I'm a part
of this, too, you know.
You probably have
a club that day.
I can skip it just this once!
[laughs]
[ASAHI]
Oh, now you can play hooky?
You've got way too much
on your plate, you know that?
[KISUMI]
No fair!
[NAGISA]
Wow, check it out!
That's from our deserted
island camp two years ago!
Sure takes me back!
Sounds like fun.
You wanna go to a
deserted island, too?
Let's do a training camp
in another country!
[NAGISA]
Ooh! Now there's an idea!
Not so fast, Nagisa.
Training camps are
serious business.
We need to take
a practical approach
and make it as
effective as we can.
We just heard back
from Samezuka Academy!
[REI]
Gou!
What did they say?
[GOU laughs] We did it,
they're totally on board!
Yahoo! I'm going to
camp with Gou!
It's not just her.
We'll be training with
the whole Iwatobi Swim Club.
And Soufuukan, too,
so there'll be three
teams in total.
That's right!
I gotta give her
some stag beetle sap.
She's gonna love it!
Hey! Are you listening, Momo?
[MOMOTARO]
Sure!
Soufuukan is where
that Capybara guy goes!
This'll be my chance to
beat him in swimming, too!
Just do me a favor
and don't get into a fight
like you did at that
resort over spring break.
Oh, I forgot!
I should probably tell Sosuke
about the training camp.
[DOCTOR 1A]
The way you've been improving,
you're definitely
ready to swim again.
[SOSUKE]
Really?
[DOCTOR 1A] Yes. Be careful
not to overwork it, though.
There is a very real risk
of damaging the area again.
And, what happens then?
You'd go back to
rehab, that's all.
Even reinjuring it
wouldn't put you
out of commission permanently.
I guess it's kinda like
I'm carrying a bomb
on my shoulder, huh?
I wouldn't say
it's that serious.
However, if you do want
to return to swimming
at your full capacity,
it's possible you'll be
forced to make a decision.
Decision?
[GOU]
Hey, Sosuke!
[SOSUKE]
Gou. You headin' home?
[GOU] Mm-hm! Just got
done with club stuff.
You on your way home, too?
Yeah, it's late.
Oh, by the way, I got a text
message from Ai earlier.
About a little training camp.
Sounds like both of our
schools are gonna be there.
Yeah, that's right!
Are we gonna see you
there, too, maybe?
Yep. I'll come along as an alum.
The doctor even
said that it's okay
for me to start swimming again.
That's wonderful!
I know! But don't mention
it to Rin yet, okay?
Huh?
It's just, I wanna
tell him myself.
[HIYORI]
Hey, I brought you some snacks.
[IKUYA]
That much?
I figured, if you
haven't eaten yet,
I might as well
make you dinner, too.
[IKUYA]
I ate already.
You don't have
to do all this stuff.
Oh, come on, at least
have some ice cream!
Want me to make some coffee?
It's okay, I can make it.
Just have a seat.
Oh, this old thing?
You held onto it, huh?
You really like this story.
You do know that everybody's
been worried about you, right?
I mean, it's pretty obvious
that you haven't been running
at your full power recently.
Like, no matter how many times
I tell everyone you're okay,
they're not buyin' it.
Captain Hoshikawa's
had his eye on you
for a while, too.
He really wants you
in that freestyle relay.
Except I don't do
relays anymore.
I know, I know.
You're at your strongest now
that you've devoted yourself
to the individual medley.
I get it.
Hiyori. You ran into my old
teammates today, didn't you?
How'd you know?
[IKUYA] I saw them nearby,
right as I was heading out.
[HIYORI] Look, I just told them
the same thing as before.
That this is a critical
time in your life,
and I don't want them
around to distract you.
That's okay, right?
[IKUYA]
I guess.
[ISANA]
That's not a great start.
[SUZUKI]
But look at that nice form!
[HIKARU]
Yeah, but what good is form
if there's no speed behind it?
What's up, Nanase?
Next to Suzuki. It's Ikuya!
Yeah, it's Ikuya Kirishima.
We're looking at me!
Sorry, but there's
just no comparison
between you and him.
[INADA] He didn't swim
in a high school tournament
over here until he came back
from the US as a third-year,
but he set a tournament record.
He only competed in the IM.
You know a lot
about him, Inada.
Well, collecting
data's my hobby!
It's kind of unusual for
someone to only swim
in the IM, though.
Actually, Ikuya was our
teammate back in middle school.
[HIKARU]
Really?
So you guys were friends?
[ASAHI] Yeah, but not
so much these days.
I feel ya.
When old friends stop
seeing each other,
they drift apart and
their friendship just dies.
I've been down that road before.
I dunno about all that.
I mean, I've moved around
a lot since I was a little kid,
and I still keep in touch
with my other friends
from back then.
Then what happened
with Kirishima?
Did you guys have a fight?
That happens a lot, too.
I wouldn't let it bug ya.
We should be putting
practice before
friendship right now, anyway.
Yeah. True.
The most important thing
is to stay focused
on getting stronger.
There's more than one way
to make yourself stronger!
[SUZUKI]
Whoa, Mikoshiba!
Everything that you
gained from the people
in your past makes you a better
version of yourself today.
Practicing's important,
but plenty of other
things in life
are more important.
All right!
It's almost time for the
general meeting to start!
[GROUP]
Right!
[ASAHI]
Guys, we're here! Sorry.
[KISUMI] Hey, what have
you two been doing?
Practice ran kinda
late, that's all.
[HARUKA]
Here.
Oh, thanks a lot, Haru.
[KISUMI] Listen, guys.
Are you sure about this?
It just seems kinda
childish to have a contest
over someone's friendship.
I don't get it.
[laughs] True, but I think
some good might come of it.
If I swim with Toono,
maybe it'll help me
understand him better.
There's something about him
that doesn't seem right.
I'm not sure what, though.
Well, I still think
it's pretty lame.
[ASAHI] The best way to learn
about someone is to swim
with them, right, Haru?
[HARUKA]
Yeah.
Hey! Not everyone's
a swimmer, you know!
[MISAKI]
Um. Don't I know you?
[MAKOTO]
Misaki?
Yeah, hi again!
[MAKOTO]
Hi! Good to see you.
[BOY 4A]
Hurry, Misaki!
'Kay! I'll be right over!
Who's that?
That's Misaki.
I met him during spring break
when I was apartment
hunting with Haru.
He had a rival
he wanted to beat,
so he was doing his best
to improve his swimming.
[MAKOTO] His coach had just
resigned out of the blue.
Since we were there, Haru and I
helped him practice a little.
Judging by the flyer,
they're still
looking for a coach.
[MAKOTO] I hope the next time
he sees that rival of his,
they'll be able to
have some fun together.
Yeah, me, too.
You're early.
Didn't think you'd show up.
[HIYORI] Well, you know,
unlike some people,
I honor my word.
Are you ready to
get started, Tachibana?
Yeah.
[IKUYA]
"The Little Mermaid."
Take your marks!
[whistle blows]
[IKUYA] "Desperate to walk
upon land, the mermaid
went to the lair of
the wicked sea witch.
In exchange for
her lovely voice,
she was granted human legs.
But when she reached the shore,
each step brought
excruciating pain,
as though 1,000 swords
were piercing her."
[ASAHI]
It's close!
Look at Makoto!
[panting]
[HIYORI]
Damn!
[IKUYA]
What about me?
What's that mean for me?
[IKUYA]
What did I gain?
And what did I
give up to get it?
[HIYORI]
There!
[BOTH panting]
You're not half bad.
[panting]
[HIYORI]
I'm impressed.
You actually put up a
pretty good fight for someone
who hasn't swum in
a while, Tachibana.
You were great, too!
I had no idea you
would be that fast.
Thanks for racing me.
You don't deserve
to speak to Ikuya,
much less be his friends.
[ASAHI] Are you--
What the hell are you saying?
[KISUMI]
Asahi.
But still, you did take
the time to race with me,
so let me tell you something
you don't know about him.
It's my gift to you.
All right, tell us.
[HIYORI] You remember
back in middle school
when he ran out of oxygen
and almost drowned?
[HIYORI]
Yeah, I figured you would.
Well, he had another
oxygen deprivation
incident in the states.
[HIYORI]
And this one was very serious.
He was in the
hospital for a while.
[MAKOTO]
Really?
[ASAHI]
No way.
[HIYORI]
Ikuya is quite delicate.
But, he eventually
overcame everything
that happened to him,
and now he's an even stronger
swimmer than he ever was before.
It's funny.
I've heard a lot
about you, Nanase,
and I've begun to
notice a pattern.
People you swim with
all seem to end up
suffering, don't they?
[HARUKA gasps]
Haru.
[HARUKA]
I...
[REI] Now it's our turn
for some action!
[NAGISA] Our joint training
camp is loaded with people!
[REI]
Next time: "An Ominous Workout!"
[NAGISA]
Let's do this!