[ROMIO]
Shizuru, milk or orange juice?
[SHIZURU]
Milk in the mornings.
[ROMIO]
Do we have enough cups?
[NAGISA]
Here's a measuring cup!
[MAKOTO chuckles]
Whoa, not so fast!
[NAGISA]
Huh? That's crazy!
[MAKOTO]
It's true.
Incredible!
You're saying it was
Haruka's first time swimming,
and he swam crawl without
even being taught how?
That's what happened.
A full 25 meters!
[ROMIO, REI, NAGISA, SHIZURU]
Huh?!
[MAKOTO]
Everyone was blown away,
even the swimming teacher.
It caused a pretty
big commotion.
[REI]
He hadn't even started school!
No way!
How come I never heard
that story before?
[MAKOTO]
I thought I mentioned it.
[REI]
How very shocking!
So, yeah.
Haru's been swimming
only freestyle
for basically his entire life.
[NAGISA]
Sounds like him!
[MAKOTO]
Well, dig in.
[ROMIO]
You're such a good cook!
[NAGISA] The toast is
kinda burnt, though.
[MAKOTO laughs]
[SHIZURU]
Are there salad bowls?
[MAKOTO]
Just use your plate.
This is it, you guys!
The first day of the All-Japan!
[MAKOTO] Mm-hm! We should head
out after we're finished eating.
I can't wait to see
Chappy's mysterious master
swim in person!
Should be fun!
[ROMIO]
I'm ready!
[NAGISA]
It's not just Haru though--
a bunch of his friends'll
be there, too!
Plus Rin!
This is a chance
for us to see some
of the greatest swimmers...
[MAKOTO]
You've come really far, Haru.
[AZUMA] Well, you startin'
to get nervous?
[HARUKA]
Not really.
[AZUMA]
Good answer.
Guess it's that time.
Yeah.
All right. Let's get breakfast.
It'll be my treat today.
[MIKHAIL] I mentioned before
that Ryuuji and I have been
rivals ever since
high school, right?
Yeah.
[MIKHAIL]
That guy was a prodigy!
Anybody could see
that he was headed
straight for the
top of the world.
"Was"? Did something happen?
A few days before the
All-Japan one year,
a close friend of his
got into a bad accident.
[RIN]
Oh.
Ryuuji could've
skipped the tournament
and hurried to his side,
but instead decided to wait
till after the race
was over to go see him.
[RIN]
Wow. How'd it go?
Not well. He lost.
It was painful for him to
sacrifice so much, only to fail.
After that, he ended up
retiring from the sport.
Seems like he's still trying
to figure out what's
truly important to him
while staying connected
to swimming in some way.
Which would explain
his working with Nanase.
To make sure that he doesn't
make the same mistakes,
or feel the same pain.
[GOU]
Hey, Makoto!
Good morning, ladies.
[GROUP]
Same to you guys.
How'd you like Suzu's place?
[ISUZU]
"Suzu"?
It wasn't very restful.
These two wouldn't let me sleep
until they'd converted me
to the muscle fandom.
[ISUZU, GOU giggle]
[MOMOTARO]
Gou!
[NITORI]
Hey, everyone.
--[NAGISA, MAKOTO] Morning!
--[REI] Good to see you.
[MOMOTARO] If I'd known
you were staying there,
I'd've stayed, too!
[ISUZU]
Yeah, like I'd let that happen.
[NAGISA]
Are we all here?
[NITORI]
Yup!
You're late, Haru.
You just got here, too.
[laughs] Touché.
[MIKHAIL]
Ryuuji! Hello--
Back off.
[MIKHAIL] Aw, can't you
be happier to see me
after all these years? [laughs]
[AZUMA] Why would I be happy
to see you, muscle-freak?
Wow! You're so quick
with the insults!
[AZUMA]
How long has it been?
[MIKHAIL]
Since the tournament in Dubai?
[AZUMA]
Yeah. I think you're right.
[MIKHAIL]
Ah, memories!
[ANNOUNCER 12A] Welcome to
day one of the 86th annual
All-Japan Invitational
Swimming Tournament.
We will begin our program
of events momentarily
with a series of
qualifying races.
[RIN]
You ready, Haru?
[CROWD cheering]
[HARUKA]
Yeah.
[NAGISA]
Here we go!
Indeed.
[AMAKATA] So anyone who
beats the base time gets
to go on to the
world championship?
Uh-huh, but it's actually
a whole lot trickier
than it sounds.
Only two swimmers can
qualify in each race.
This is a totally
different level than
the other tournaments
we've been to.
No kidding?
[sighs] So remind me.
Today is Haru's 200-meter free,
Rin's 100-meter butterfly,
and Asahi and Toono's
50-meter freestyle, right?
Yeah, and don't
forget about Ikuya--
[ANNOUNCER 12A]
The qualifier for the men's
200-meter individual medley
will begin in a moment.
Man, the big day
is finally here.
Sure is.
It's Ikuya...
against his brother!
[NATSUYA laughing]
[IKUYA]
Would you stop laughing?
[NATSUYA] Sorry. I just
never expected this.
Y'know I kinda wish
I could go back
and tell my middle-school self,
"One day, when you're
all grown up,
you're gonna compete in the
All-Japan against your brother."
I wish I could, too.
Wonder if I'd believe me.
[NATSUYA]
Don't you dare hold back.
Me, hold back? You wish.
Well, you two, good luck.
[ANNOUNCER 12A]
Take your marks.
--[beep]
--[CROWD] Go!
[ASAHI]
Whoa! Natsuya's fast!
You got this.
[MAKOTO] Look at that!
Ikuya's closing in on him!
[MIKHAIL] Hey, Natsuya's
little brother's got talent!
That's what I call totes
hip with the kids!
[WOMAN 12A giggles]
Hear that?
[gasps] Ryuuji!
They're even.
It's way too close to call.
[panting]
Come on! Catch me!
[TERASHIMA] Whoa! He's picking
up speed this far in?
[HIYORI]
All right! He's catching up!
They're both amazing!
--Yeah!
--Go!
--[IKUYA panting]
--[NATSUYA panting]
[CROWD cheers]
[HIYORI]
He did it!
Way to go!
Good for him.
[panting]
[NATSUYA]
Look at you.
You really have grown up a lot.
[IKUYA]
Natsuya.
Thanks.
[IKUYA]
Ah! Hey!
[NATSUYA] I guess you got strong
while I had my back turned.
I mean it when I say this.
Little bro, I'm proud of you.
[gasps]
Well, how could I not succeed?
When I have a big brother
like you to look up to.
[AZUMA]
Their times were pretty decent,
but it might not be
good enough. It's cutthroat.
Exactly.
They'd better not get
too confident just yet.
--Seijuurou!
--[ISUZU] Go!
Captain Hoshikawa!
[SHIMOGAMI SWIMMER 12A]
You can do it, man!
[MIKOSHIBA grunts]
Damnit.
Not enough.
He should've qualified.
Yeah, he's so fast.
The two guys who did make it
must be older than we are!
--[beep]
--It's scary. Huh, Rei?
Very. This world
they're in now--
it's even more intense than
I imagined it would be.
[HIYORI]
As I recall, you and I tied
in the 50-meter freestyle
the last time.
Uh-huh.
Now's our chance to settle
the score once and for all!
I've been practicing
my butt off to get ready
for this race with you, so...
[ASAHI]
What's his problem?
So he's really here.
Kaede Kinjou from Naribusawa.
That guy?
[ANNOUNCER 12A]
Take your marks.
--[beep]
--[CROWD] Go!
Asahi!
Wow, that Kinjou guy's
unbelievably strong!
[panting]
[ASAHI]
Damn it!
Did he just break
a tournament record?
Who goes all out in a qualifier?
[AZUMA]
What's wrong? You look scared.
I'm not.
You can't get that good without
throwing something away.
No one can survive in
the competitive world
with a regular mindset.
The only people who can
make it at that level
are those who don't
waver an inch,
even for the sake of those
they care about most.
Next race up is the
men's 100-meter butterfly.
[BOTH]
Come on, Rin!
[whistle blowing]
Do your best.
[ANNOUNCER 12A]
Take your marks.
--[beep]
--[CROWD] Go!
That start wasn't too bad.
In this one heat alone,
three guys have been to
the world championships.
Come on.
[NITORI]
He picked up speed!
All right, Rin!
I think...
He might...
Let's go!
[gasps]
[CROWD cheers]
Second place!
It looks like he just barely
beat the qualifying time.
Yay!
Rin. I'm so proud.
[gasps] Yeah!
It's your turn next.
You better get ready.
Right.
[ANNOUNCER 12A] Men's
200-meter freestyle. Final.
This race could change
his entire life!
[MAKOTO]
Yeah.
[sighs]
[ANNOUNCER 12]
Lane five, Haruka Nanase,
Hidaka University.
Haru.
[ANNOUNCER 12A]
Take your marks.
--[beep]
--[CROWD] Go!
That idiot.
A late start!
--[REI] Come on, Haruka!
--[NAGISA] You can do it!
His movement's kinda rough.
Oh, no.
--[MAKOTO] Haru!
--[KISUMI] Hurry!
[CROWD gasps]
No way, did he just lose?
[panting]
[NAGISA whines]
Poor Haru!
He still has the 100-meter
freestyle race tomorrow.
[KISUMI] It's too bad you
didn't make the cut, Asashi.
[ASAHI] Yeah, but I still
feel good about it.
Besides, I'll get another
chance in tomorrow's butterfly!
And if I lose in that,
there's always next year, right?
You're getting a little
ahead of yourself.
You really are exactly
the same person
you were in middle
school, aren't you?
Aw, come on, enough
with the compliments,
you're makin' me blush!
Didn't sound like he was
trying to compliment you.
Ugh.
[SOSUKE]
Rin.
Congrats on the
100-meter butterfly.
Thanks! Feels good.
On to the world stage, huh?
I guess so, I'm not really
sure how much farther
I'll get, but gonna try my best!
Oh, and I still have the
100-meter freestyle, too.
Yeah, that's true.
Against Haru, Ikuya Kirishima,
and Kaede Kinjou.
That's crazy.
I dunno why, but I'm more
excited than nervous.
That's a good sign.
I hope I can swim
in a race like that soon.
[RIN]
Yeah.
Hurry up and get back
in the game, Sosuke.
Hey, Haru, over here! Come on!
[REI]
Great swimming today!
[NAGISA] We're about
to go get dinner with Ai
and the other guys.
You wanna come?
[HARUKA] Nah. I should
probably get some air.
[NAGISA] Oh, okay. Well,
good luck tomorrow!
We'll be here rooting for you!
[HARUKA]
Thanks, I appreciate it.
Guys, let's go!
[NAGISA laughs] We should
head out. See ya later!
[REI]
Do your best tomorrow, Haruka!
[HARUKA]
Mm-hm.
[NAGISA]
Bye, Mako, Asahi, Ikuya!
And it was nice
meeting you, Hiyo!
Later, Kissme!
"Hiyo"?
Come on, my name's Kisumi!
[IKUYA] Well, see you
in the 100-meter free.
I guess so.
[ASAHI]
You got this, guys!
I have total faith
in both of you!
Oh, and good luck
in the butterfly.
You'll do great.
Don't think I've
forgotten about your
100-meter breaststroke, man.
I'll be cheering
for that one, too!
Great, thanks a lot, Asahi.
[TERASHIMA]
Kirishima, Toono!
What's the holdup? We gotta go!
[HIYORI]
We'll be right there!
'Kay, See ya.
[HIYORI]
Till tomorrow, then.
[ASAHI]
Yup!
Well, I guess I better
be heading home, too.
G'night, guys.
Yeah, have a good one.
[KISUMI]
Bye!
[ASAHI] Oh, hey, could you
give me a ride, Kisumi?
So, uh.
[RIN]
There you are.
[MAKOTO]
Rin!
What's up? Are you two
the only ones still here?
Just us.
Hey, good job on the butterfly!
Oh, yeah. Thank you.
The way you hung in
there at the very end?
Impressive!
[RIN laughs] I'm really worn
out from it now, though.
But, next the real fight begins.
Since we're all here,
what do you say we go
cool off for a little bit?
[RIN]
Eh...
And I know just the
place we should go.
[MAKOTO] It's funny, I haven't
been this close to the ocean
since I moved here.
Coach said I'd have to
throw something away.
But I didn't really
wanna do that.
[HARUKA]
And then I lost.
I've been thinking
about it since the race.
Maybe this means
that I don't deserve
to compete internationally.
[RIN, MAKOTO laugh]
What's so funny?
Nothin'.
Just thinkin' about
how even you're
feelin' the pressure now.
Seems like this thing's
got you all fired up.
Yeah, you're the reason
we're all here.
Your swimming inspires us.
I think the fact that
you're worried about it...
That's your answer.
[RIN]
Heh.
I don't get it.
Look, Haru.
I've had so many
pressures in life--
I thought they'd crush me.
I didn't always
believe in myself.
[RIN] Hah. Guess you
know that, though.
But, after all of our
struggling and butting heads,
somehow, we overcame everything
and made it this far.
There's more than one
way to chase a dream.
[RIN] So, I say we face
tomorrow head-on!
That sound good?
You know, now that I've
worked with those kids,
I know I wanna be a trainer!
[RIN]
Yeah?
[MAKOTO] I've been watching
them go head-to-head
in pursuit of their dreams,
and that showed me
that there's a lot more I
wanna do in the future.
I can't wait to see
where life takes me!
So now, my goal is
to help swimmers
who aim for the top.
If I do, maybe that will open
doors for me to teach kids
how fun swimming is, too.
Wow, that's a beautiful dream.
And, of course,
I wanna keep supporting
you guys, also.
I mean, what could be cooler
than getting to have more
moments like this again?
[RIN]
Heh. Yeah, I agree.
I'm rootin' for you, Makoto.
[MAKOTO]
I appreciate it.
[MAKOTO, RIN gasp]
[inhales]
[yells]
[HARUKA]
Bring it on, world!
[RIN]
Uh-- Haru.
[laughs] Come on, Rin,
let's go, too!
Uh-- What is this?
Some kinda teen drama?
Wait up!
[MIKHAIL] There's still a lot
of tight races waiting for them
in this tournament.
Those kids are so young.
The pressure must be enormous.
They just need more
strength of mind.
Dammit. That Nanase.
He was so close to going
to the world championships.
But did you notice?
[AZUMA]
Yeah.
I think that bad start
really sapped his strength
at the beginning of the race.
Toward the halfway point,
though, it was clear
that his speed was
greater than Albert's.
[MIKHAIL] But then,
he slowed down at the end.
My guess is that
he had his mind
on something else, and it
wasn't Albert or Kinjou.
I think he faltered at
the feeling of surpassing
his limits in freestyle.
That kid's got so much
untapped potential,
it's kinda terrifying.
I think Rin- kun 's right
up there with him, though.
[AZUMA]
Hmph! We'll see tomorrow.
He won't stop talking
about stupid crap
like friendship and bonds.
[MIKHAIL]
Times change, Ryuuji.
Who knows what direction
their lives will take next?
[HIYORI]
He beat the base time by a mile.
That's a tournament record
in 100-meter freestyle.
This guy's insane.
[ANNOUNCER 12A] Men's 100-meter
freestyle qualifier,
fourth heat.
[RIN]
So? How do you feel?
[HARUKA]
I'm surprisingly calm.
[RIN laughs]
I'm psyched.
The whole world's ahead of us.
It's kinda like a dream.
[HARUKA]
No. This is real.
[RIN]
Yeah, you're right.
It's so close, we can
reach out and touch it.
Nobody knows what's gonna
happen from here on out.
It's a mystery.
[HARUKA] Whatever's ahead.
I'm ready to face it.
[RIN]
Me, too! It's time to dive.
[RIN, HARUKA]
To the future!
[CROWD]
Go!
[TV ANNOUNCER 12A] Nanase's
still leading at the turn!
[TV ANNOUNCER 12B] Looks like
he's setting an excellent pace!
[TV ANNOUNCER 12A]
If this keeps up, we'll have
a new tournament record.