[TOMO]
Hey there! You live around here?
Who are you?
Uh--
I'm, um...
[TOMO]
It's not a hard question.
[GIRL 6A]
Tomo! Come play house with us!
I'll be right there!
[HIYORI] When I was a little
kid, I was alone all the time.
[MOM 6A] Aw, are you
by yourself, Hiyo?
[MOM 6B] Are your parents
both working again today?
[MOM 6C]
You do so well on your own!
[MOMS]
What a big boy!
[HIYORI]
Really, I hated being alone.
But I always smiled anyway.
Hiyori, sweetie.
It turns out your
father and I both
have to work again
this Sunday. Sorry.
I'll be okay, Mom!
[HIYORI]
I had to keep on smiling.
I needed to be the kind
of kid grown-ups liked.
[HIYORI] So I tried to
act the way I thought
they would want me to.
[HIYORI]
Anytime I was around people,
I was focused on playing a part.
But, whenever I was in the
water, those were the times
I felt the most like myself.
[sighs]
--[giggles]
--[HIYORI gasps]
Uh...
[HIYORI] And that's where
I first met Ikuya.
Hey. You're really good
at swimming, aren't you?
Uh, thank you.
Do you wanna swim together?
[HIYORI]
Uh!
Sure!
[HIYORI]
That was the day when I learned
how to smile for real again.
[IKUYA]
Was it slow?
[panting]
My free sucks today.
Ready to go?
[TERASHIMA]
Kirishima, up for some karaoke?
You still haven't heard
my awesome singing!
Yeah, right! It's more
like dancing and yodeling!
He's all, "yo-de-lay-hee-hoo!"
You think that's cool.
I do it while I'm swimming, too.
Amazing!
So? You coming?
No thanks. I'm kinda busy today.
--Wait up--
--[HOSHIKAWA] Hey, Toono.
I see you're not just
a backstroke swimmer.
Your 50-meter free's
improved, too.
So, next tournament,
I think you should do--
Sorry, Captain.
I'll have to get back
to you on that, okay?
[HIYORI]
Hold on, Ikuya!
[IKUYA]
I know it's stupid to get mad
just because my time got worse.
But I can't let anyone
see me acting so weak.
I have to get stronger.
You're still obsessing
over Nanase, aren't you?
It's not hard to figure
out why you've been
struggling in freestyle.
I've told you about
all this before.
In middle school, when I had
that accident during practice.
Haru came to save
me just in time.
But then,
I got really upset when he
quit and the team split up.
[IKUYA] I guess I decided
to keep swimming because...
...I just couldn't stand still.
I really believed, if I gave
him some time, he'd come back.
Then I went to America.
And, well... You know
what happened.
[IKUYA] As I sank through
the water all alone,
I thought, "Wow.
Haru's gone for good."
[IKUYA]
And that wasn't all.
I realized how weak
I was for relying
on my brother and my
teammates all the time.
That I'm the only person
who has the power
to make myself stronger.
[IKUYA]
I had to do it all alone.
But then, when I saw him again,
the weakness I thought
I left behind
came flooding back to me.
[IKUYA]
And I just can't allow myself
to be that vulnerable right now.
Sorry. I'm going home.
Ikuya...
Damn.
[HIYORI] Is there anything
I can do for him?
[IKUYA]
Hey, nice swimming!
Really? Um. Well, thank you.
Huh? Wait a second!
[HIYORI gasps]
I'm, uh!
Hiyori Toono.
My name's Ikuya.
[IKUYA]
Did you come here to train?
[HIYORI] Nah. We had to move
because of my parents' work.
Oh, yeah?
[HIYORI]
But in grade school.
I actually lived in Iwatobi.
Hey! Me, too!
That's where I lived before
I came to the states!
That's so cool.
I wonder if we've met before.
Um. Yeah.
[NATSUYA]
There you are.
Oh. Hey!
That's my brother.
No! Ikuya!
[gasps]
[HIYORI]
Come on. Wake up!
Here. I really enjoyed these.
Thanks, but, I'm not
much of a reader.
Uh, sorry.
I bet you must be
pretty smart, though.
'Cause all of these books
look super complicated.
Thank you.
Except I guess there is
one book I've always liked.
Is there really? Which one?
There's this mermaid.
[gasps]
What? Well don't
get creeped out!
[HIYORI]
Uh--
You think it's girly, don't you?
No, that's not what
I was thinking! Really!
Just-- I-I--
It's okay. Relax,
you can stop panicking.
[IKUYA chuckles]
[door opens]
[NATSUYA] What's up?
Looks like you're havin' fun.
Oh, hey.
[NATSUYA] Thanks for spending
so much time with him.
Sure thing.
[NATSUYA] And of course,
thanks for saving h--
I should really
be going now.
Bye.
See ya later!
[HIYORI]
Yep.
How can I... help him?
[GIRL 6B]
Come on, Mom! Read me the rest!
[MOM 6E]
Where did we leave off?
[GIRL 6B] Right after
the little mermaid saves
the handsome prince and they
end up on the seashore!
[MOM 6E] "Having rescued
the prince from drowning,
the mermaid brought him
to rest on the sand.
Just then, along came
a young human maiden.
Thinking quickly, the mermaid
concealed herself from sight.
When the prince awakened,
he believed the maiden
standing before him
had been his savior.
So he expressed his
gratitude to her."
[MOM 6E]
"He had no idea what the mermaid
had just done for him.
And so, the maiden was--"
[HIYORI]
That's right.
The prince still doesn't
know the truth.
[MAKOTO] I never expected
I'd run into you here, Nao.
Me neither!
How long have you
been coaching here?
It's my first day.
It all started
during spring break,
when I met that
little guy on a trip
to pick out Haru's apartment.
He's serious about swimming.
I wanted to help out
more kids like that.
So, you're both goin'
to school here in Tokyo?
Yep! Asahi, too.
They're at Hidaka though.
You're all together
again--that's wonderful!
I take it the two of them
are still swimming, as well?
[MAKOTO]
Mm! Yeah. They are.
But I'm in the sports
education department.
So I don't swim much.
Oh. Then you and I are similar.
I've been majoring
in sports medicine.
I want a job where I can
support other swimmers,
so I'm working to
become a trainer.
[NAO] Oh, wow! You three
really have grown up!
You look like you're
a lot tougher now.
How've you been?
Not too bad.
[AKANE]
I hear you were Asahi's manager
when he was in middle school.
I sure hope he didn't cause
you too much trouble.
Cut it out! Stop
treating me like a baby!
Still a little on the
sensitive side, huh?
[ASAHI] Aw! Jeez,
leave it alone, already!
[laughs] What's
Ikuya been up to?
Have you kept in touch?
[NAO] Natsuya says he's
back from America,
going to college in Tokyo.
[MAKOTO] Yeah, he's at
Shimogami University now.
Actually, we just saw him
for the first time in years
at a newcomer tournament.
Oh, that's great!
Isn't it?
I guess, but it seems he's
not doing so great lately.
[NAO]
What happened?
It was my fault.
That's what Ikuya's
teammate said, at least.
People I swim with always
seem to end up suffering.
Oh...
Man! That's such a load of crap!
Makoto and I have swum with you
and you don't see us
suffering, do ya?
[MAKOTO chuckles]
We wanna make this right.
But we're not sure how.
Can't you just talk to him?
Well, Toono--
That's the teammate
we mentioned.
It seems he doesn't want
Ikuya anywhere near Haru.
I see. Okay, then.
I'll see what Natsuya
can tell me.
But still. Based on
everything you just told me,
I feel like there's
more you guys can do
to improve the situation.
[gasps]
[NAO] Just my opinion as
your former teammate. 'Kay?
[HARUKA, ASAHI, MAKOTO]
Right.
[HIYORI]
Look, I found a great café.
[IKUYA]
Yeah, colorful.
Let's go on the way home.
[IKUYA] Sorry. I'm not
in the mood today.
That's fine.
It'll still be there whenever
you feel up to it.
[IKUYA]
Hm.
[HIYORI]
Hey, didn't the little mermaid
turn into seafoam at the end?
You know, in that story
you like so much.
I'm not too fond
of it, actually.
She stayed right by
the prince's side
throughout everything,
and yet...
Hey, something wrong?
Of course not.
[ASAHI]
So good!
What gives?
Is it National No-Mackerel Day?
That's not a thing.
[AZUMA] What'd I tell you
knuckleheads about mackerel?
Listen up. The hot dish
here is Tanuki soba.
This guy again?
What, are you some
kinda cafeteria foodie?
Yup. Got a blog and everything.
[ASAHI]
Sorry I asked.
[AZUMA]
Hey, you. Remember a while back,
I wanted to know why
you only swim free.
Got an answer for me yet?
Unless you discover
it for yourself,
your potential's gonna
stay locked up forever.
You still haven't
told us who you are.
[ASAHI] You're not just
a food critic, are you?
Right now, all I wanna do is
get my blog ranking higher.
Be sure to click the heart
button if you like my stuff.
I'm not "hearting"
anything for you!
[KON]
Hey, Asahi.
What's up, Kon?
Hey, Haru, this is
my sister's husband.
The sports journalist
I told you about.
Kon Kurimiya.
Working?
Kinda-sorta.
Hey, uh. How do you know Ryuuji?
Wait, who's Ryuuji?
Oh! That old guy with the coat?
Well yeah, he's...
[MIKHAIL]
I can't get over how many
great Japanese
proverbs there are!
Like, "Time is muscle!"
Ooh! And, uh...
"One day, your muscles
won't be around!"
And "Muscle is the key
to every door."
Which one is your
favorite, Rin- kun ?
[RIN] Uh, I don't
have a preference.
Rin- kun . Please.
They say, "Those who
laugh at muscle
will one day cry over muscle."
[gasps]
[RIN]
Who is that?
[MIKHAIL]
Well, now!
Looks like they're
watching a video
of one of my high
school tournaments.
No way.
[MIKHAIL]
What's this?
Could it be that you're
captivated by my impressive
muscles I had back in my prime?
[RIN]
Those strokes are really bold!
[MIKHAIL]
You think I was powerful--
look at the fellow
swimming next to me.
[KON]
That's Ryuuji.
Actually, they used to call
him "Fully-Built Ryuuji"
in those days.
An unbelievable swimmer,
he had insane competitive
talent at the global level.
That old geezer?
[KON] Yeah, but he gave up
competitive swimming
out of nowhere for some reason.
I heard he was coaching
overseas after his retirement.
All the swimmers who
train under him
tend to pile on a ton of muscle.
So now people have
taken to calling him
"Pile-It-On Ryuuji."
The rumors said he
was back in Japan.
I wonder if he's planning
to work as a coach here, too?
[NATSUYA]
It's been a while.
I'm back in Japan
for a little bit.
[HIYORI]
Oh, that's good to hear.
[NATSUYA]
How's Ikuya doing?
[HIYORI gasps]
I tried calling his phone,
but I'm having a hard
time getting through.
[HIYORI] Well, he's upset that
his time's not improving.
[NATSUYA]
Is it worse?
It's nothin' to worry about.
If I know him, he'll bounce
back from this in no time.
He just missed
your calls because
he's focusing on
training, I guess.
[NATSUYA]
Probably.
He always has been
the type to forget
about what's going
on around him.
Just make sure he doesn't
push himself too hard, okay?
I can't go through that again.
Sure.
[MISAKI]
Wow, this looks yummy!
College must be so awesome!
[laughs] So he wasn't
just a cafeteria critic.
He used to swim competitively?
Uh, Haru?
[HARUKA] He asked why I refuse
to swim anything but free,
and I still haven't
stopped thinking about it.
I just... I don't
know how to answer.
Tricky.
[MISAKI] Then you should
start swimming other stuff.
[gasps]
[MAKOTO gasps]
Uh-- What'd I say?
[HIYORI]
All his strokes are worse.
Back, butterfly,
even his breaststroke,
and that's his best one!
But... especially freestyle.
[KON] Why do you think Ryuuji
was roaming around Hidaka U?
[AKANE]
He's a coach, right?
If you ask me,
he found a prospect.
[KON]
Hm.
[doorbell chimes]
Hello, sir, welcome in.
Well, speak of the devil.
[gasps]
[HIYORI]
Ikuya?
You okay?
I can't see the stars.
[IKUYA]
I could see them that night.
By the pool. Haru and me.
In the sky, in the water.
As we made that
promise together.
Stars were falling everywhere.
[IKUYA] I felt like
my wish would come true.
Like I had been set free.
[IKUYA]
But, I was wrong.
I was as weak as I ever was.
I told you, you're not.
I know if I sink again,
there won't be
anyone there to rescue me.
Which is why it's up to me
to make myself stronger.
And why I trained so hard.
You have the skill
to take on the world.
To compete globally!
[IKUYA]
That's not true. I'm a weakling.
[HIYORI]
No, you're wrong!
You're a lot stronger
than you were!
You can become everything
that you wanna be--I know it!
To make your wish come true,
you don't need shooting stars!
[IKUYA] "In exchange
for her lovely voice,
the little mermaid gained legs,
and excruciating pain."
I traded away my heart
to gain strength.
Or so I thought.
But, I still didn't
get to be human.
[HIYORI] Stop it! You're not
the little mermaid, Ikuya!
I should just accept
that I'll never be
strong like Haru.
[IKUYA gasps]
Would you forget about
Nanase already?
I can't bear to see you
suffering because of him.
I won't tolerate it!
What I choose to think
about is my decision.
You could be in
worldwide competition.
I know you can! You can
become a whole new you!
And if that'll make you
happy, then I'll do any--
[IKUYA] Shut up! You don't
understand at all!
Don't act like you do!
[HIYORI grunts]
[HIYORI]
You're not yourself anymore.
Not since you saw him.
I wish you'd just get him
out of your life for good.
Ikuya. You're the
one who's confused!
Why can't you see that
the best thing for you
is to let him go?!
Look. It's none of your
damn business, okay?!
[HIYORI gasps]
Sorry.
Ikuya...
Here he is, workin' hard.
[REI] We seek strength because
we need to feel safe.
[NAGISA] But sometimes,
strength becomes weakness.
[REI] Next time:
"A Solitary Medley!"
[NAGISA]
Time for a tournament!