[REI] Tokyo really is
as crowded as they say.
[ROMIO]
Right?
It's always like this around
Hachiko in the summertime.
But the Moyai statue's a good
place to meet up, too,
if you're trying
to avoid the crowds.
[laughs] I get why you say
Tokyo's your second home--
you could give tours!
[GOU]
This place is great.
[GOU, AYUMU gulp]
There're muscles
all over the place!
And more!
Wow. Hachiko.
[MAKOTO]
Hey!
Mako!
Sorry to hold you up!
It's fine--we just got here!
Wait, where's Rei?
[NAGISA]
He went to the bathroom.
That's the evil king who
wanted the magic lamp.
[MAKOTO]
Hm? Oh.
You guys must be the
new club members.
[ROMIO]
Romio Hayafune!
[AYUMU]
Ayumu Kunikida!
[SHIZURU]
Shizuru Isurugi.
I've heard a lot
about you three.
Hi, I'm Makoto Tachibana.
Pleasure's mine.
[ALL gasp]
[ROMIO, AYUMU, SHIZURU]
We're honored to meet you!
[REI] It's such a delight
to catch up with you!
[MAKOTO]
Yeah, long time no see.
How've you been doing?
[REI]
Quite well!
[NAGISA] Haru's at his
training camp today, isn't he?
He's been trying to get
more practice in,
since the All-Japan's
almost here.
So the nationals start tomorrow.
You feelin' ready?
Yes!
I'm butterfly and
Nagisa's breaststroke.
It's all so exciting!
[MAKOTO] Mm-hm! Rei. Nagisa.
I'm proud of you guys.
I'm sorry you two
didn't make the cut,
but we can still go
cheer on your teammates!
[BOTH]
Sir!
[NAGISA] I'm just sad
we couldn't see Haru.
[REI]
There's no helping it, Nagisa.
The All-Japan Invitational
is next week,
and that is a pivotal time
in any swimmer's career!
[NAGISA]
I guess you're right.
Didn't you tell us that
your older brother
is doing some
extra training, too?
Yeah, but he and Haruka
are working with
different coaches,
so they aren't going to be
practicing together or anything.
[NAGISA]
Hm.
[REI] It's inspiring to see
everyone working so hard
toward their goals.
I suggest we do the same!
And the first step to
that is a good meal!
Let's eat!
[ALL]
Sounds good!
[MIKHAIL] Mm! I can't tell you
how much I love Japanese food!
Your muscles appear to be
in excellent condition,
by the way.
I feel like sashimi that
found its way to water!
I don't think sashimi
has any business
in the water, Coach.
[MIKHAIL]
Oh, almost forgot!
He's probably on break, too.
Shouldn't you answer that?
[sighs]
Yeah, what?
[MIKHAIL]
Ryuuji, finally!
How long has it been?
I tried calling you
a million times,
but it wasn't going through.
'Cause I was ignoring you.
[laughs] You are as unfriendly
as you've always been, I see!
Listen, I'm busy here.
You mind gettin' to the point?
Just want to say I'm in Japan.
I hear you've been coaching
someone who's competing
in the All-Japan Invitational.
How do you know about that?
'Cause I know everything
about you, obviously.
But here's the kicker.
I'm also training a swimmer
who's in the All-Japan--
isn't that something?
If we'd seen his rad
muscles back in our day,
he would've given you
a run for your money!
Look, Mikhail.
I've got a quick word
of advice to give you.
What's that?
I know that you're a
little behind the times,
but no one says the
word "rad" anymore.
[gasps] Really?
Really, but here's
a phrase that'll
make you sound extra cool.
You should say "I'm totes
hip with the kids, yo!"
"Totes hip with the kids,"
I think I can do that.
You're the best, Ryuuji!
I'll be sure to master it
before the All-Japan Invi--
That one of your friends?
More like a fungus that
I've been stuck with
since high school.
Someone from Iwatobi?
Nah, different school.
We met each other competing
at the nationals one year.
He's actually Russian,
but he was living
here at the time.
Now that I think about it,
the high school nationals
will be starting tomorrow.
Isn't Iwatobi going?
[gasps]
[REI]
What a lovely meal!
[MAKOTO] Sorry, everyone.
I gotta get goin'.
My shift starts soon,
and I don't wanna be late.
But, this has been fun!
Besides your classes,
you're also coaching
at a swim club. Right?
Yeah. Oh, hey! Since
you guys are here,
why don't you come
by for a swim?
[ALL gasp]
Sure thing!
[gasps]
[MAKOTO]
Romio and Shizuru.
They have opposite styles,
but they're equally good.
If they keep on improving,
then I think they'll
both be going places
by next year.
Yeah, Romio's been
regularly attending
a swimming club ever since
he was in elementary school.
And Shizu kinda does
things his own way,
but he's got natural talent!
I can't wait to see
how far they go.
[REI]
I agree. They're inspiring!
[NAGISA laughs]
You said it!
So, you are ready, Rei?
Of course! It's my first
time at the nationals.
I could not be readier!
Yeah, he's been
training really hard.
We're so proud of him!
I appreciate your
support, Nagisa.
The Iwatobi Swim Club has
accomplished quite a lot
during the last three years.
Let's show them what we've got!
[NAGISA]
Mm-hm!
[REI] I'm kind of nervous,
but I have faith in our team.
All we can do is
our best, right?
[NAGISA] Roger that!
Let's get some practice in!
[GOU] Hold on, Nagisa! You're
supposed to warm up first!
[KON]
How's Nanase doing?
[AZUMA]
Hm? Eh, fine.
[KON] Not too long ago, I wrote
a story about that Kinjou kid,
from Naribusawa.
Man, talk about potential.
He had already gotten
a lot of buzz
as a butterfly swimmer,
but ever since he switched
to freestyle, he's been
making insane progress.
It's not official or anything,
but during practice yesterday,
the guy beat the
national record.
[AZUMA] Sounds like we've got
another monster on the scene.
I figured you'd be at least
a little interested.
So what's the deal?
[AZUMA] Yeah, I'm just bored
with swimmers who have
nothing to offer outside
of brute strength.
The champs
are the ones who fight
like their lives
are depending on it.
[MOMOTARO]
Yahoo! I can't wait!
[NITORI] Let's give it our best
in there so we can go home
with no regrets!
[SAMEZUKA SWIMMERS]
Right!
[NAGISA]
Ai! Momo!
Hey!
[MOMOTARO]
It's Gou!
Did you guys come to
check out the venue, too?
Yes. This is our last
high school meet,
so we're trying to be as
prepared for it as possible.
It was too bad how that relay
at regionals turned out.
Yeah, your swimming
that day was amazing.
Ah! Really? Thank you so much!
[SHIZURU]
For you.
Fancy fish?
No way! I want some!
[SHIZURU]
Go ahead.
[UOZUMI] Whoa, sweet! That's
really thoughtful of you!
I guess I'll be
competing against you
in the breaststroke, huh?
That's right, and I hope
you're ready to face me, Nagisa.
Because my plan is to apply
everything I've learned
in the last three years of
training to this one race.
Oh, I'm ready. Let's go.
[ISUZU]
Momotaro!
[gasps] Hey, sis!
Wait, what?
Those two are siblings?
What are you up to, Momo?
Um. Scopin' the place out?
[gasps] You're so cute!
You must be Iwatobi's
famous Gou!
Um, hi?
[ISUZU]
I'm Isuzu Mikoshiba!
It's nice to meet ya.
Both my brothers talk
about you all the time!
Oh. I wonder what they've said.
Aw, come on, sis, Gou
thinks I'm really cool,
please don't ruin it!
[ISUZU] Is it true your
brother Rin's muscles
are the stuff of legends?
[GOU gasps]
Are his pecs really so
enormous that he has cleavage?
Can it be you understand?
Yes.
Hey, I heard that Nanase's
attending a training
camp right now
to get ready for the
All-Japan Invitational.
He is.
So, unfortunately, it seems
highly doubtful he'll be able
to make it here
for tomorrow's races.
I understand. This is a really
important time for him.
And for Rin, too.
I'm sure he's working
extremely hard.
[REI]
Yes, I'm sure.
[panting]
[AZUMA]
I think we should call it a day.
See ya. Don't forget
your cooldowns.
Coach Azuma.
[phone ringing]
Hey, Haru.
There's somethin' I wanted
to talk to you about.
[HARUKA] Sure. I wanted
to talk to you, too.
[REI] It's finally here.
My last high school summer.
Where'd Rei go?
[AMAKATA]
We meet again, Tokyo.
Where there once
was a barren desert,
now stands a city of hope.
[SASABE]
Huh? Hey! Nagisa!
Hey, it's Coach!
We thought we'd come
and cheer you guys on.
It is your big moment in
the spotlight, after all!
[SASABE laughs]
[KISUMI] Don't you think we
got here a little too early?
[laughs] I guess after
that close call last time,
I was worried about
being too late.
I dunno, you guys,
I didn't even go
to that high school.
Come on, don't be like that!
At least you get to spend
time with your friends!
[KISUMI] But, wait, you didn't
go to their high school either.
[ASAHI] I know, but I
wanna cheer on the guys
from my old school.
There you are. Come on, get in.
[HARUKA]
Coach Mikhail let you leave?
Sure.
But, look, if this throws
off your condition,
you can't blame me,
you got that?
I'm not that fragile.
A single day off isn't
gonna undo everything.
Still pretty cocky, aren't ya?
Same goes for you.
[HARUKA]
Hey, you're driving too fast.
[AZUMA] Damn, it's almost
time for the All-Japan,
and this knucklehead
changes his whole schedule
to go support his old teammates?
Who the hell does that?
[MAKOTO]
Look at all the people!
Guess it's a good thing
we got here early.
[ASAHI]
There they are!
Okay, I'll catch up
with you guys later!
[MAKOTO]
Mm-hm!
[NAGISA]
Mako! You're here!
Sure am. Hey, guys.
You're so early!
I know. I couldn't
sleep for some reason.
[NAGISA laughs] That's weird,
you're not even swimming today!
[MAKOTO]
Right? I don't get it.
[RIN] So did you tell Rei
and Nagisa you were coming?
Nope.
Yeah, I haven't told
any of my guys either.
Well, this kind of thing is more
fun if it's a surprise, right?
Isuzu!
I can't believe there's
another Mikoshiba.
She's got some
serious power! Plus...
[gasps]
[UOZUMI]
She's hot!
Yahoo! That's my sister!
That was a great race.
Yeah, I know, right?
Did you come to see us?
Yeah.
And there's something
I wanna tell you.
[KISUMI]
Asahi still isn't back.
Well, I'm sure he
and his old buddies
had a lot of catching up to do.
Hey, where's Rei, though?
He was saying he
needed some fresh air,
so he went outside
for a few minutes.
[ASAHI] You guys look so much
older now, it's crazy!
[INUHIKO]
You okay? What's wrong?
Nothing. I just zoned out.
[RIN]
Damnit! We're so close, too!
Hey, look.
[HARUKA]
We can just park in there.
Huh? But, it's way too far!
No, it'll be faster if we run.
[laughs] Don't you think this
is a bit dumb for us to do
right before the All-Japan?
It's not dumb. It's just free.
[laughs]
This isn't like me.
Okay.
Guess I better get back to
the people I came here with.
I'll text you guys.
See ya later!
[KAZAMI SWIMMERS]
Bye!
[BOTH]
Hey! Aren't you--?
[ASAHI] I can't believe you
still wear those red glasses!
[REI]
Yes. Hold on.
If you're here, that must
mean you've kept up
with swimming all these years!
Well, no. You're in
street clothes, so.
You're here to watch?
Uh-huh!
I gotta support my
high school team, right?
I just started my
first year of college.
And yup, I'm still a swimmer!
I'm gonna compete in
the butterfly race myself.
[ASAHI] Whoa! No kidding?
That's awesome!
I didn't even make it to
the nationals in high school!
So I'm guessing that's
the reason you look like
you're about to throw up, huh?
Uh-- I'm not nervous!
There are a lot of ways
to prepare yourself
mentally for this kind of stuff.
But try not to think
about it too much, okay?
[ASAHI]
Victory's tricky.
You just gotta make or break it!
I don't wanna break
anything, though.
[ASAHI laughs]
It's a figure of speech.
My point is, part of
winning is always luck,
and it seems like you've
got some of the best
luck in the world!
I mean look, here we are,
after all this time.
And we ran into each other
today, of all days.
That's true.
Maybe you have a point there.
Hey, forget the maybe!
Have some faith! You got this!
'Kay?
Right!
[HARUKA, RIN panting]
[CROWD cheering]
[ANNOUNCER 11A]
The qualifier for the men's
100-meter butterfly
will now begin.
We made it just in time.
[HARUKA]
Good.
[RIN] Okay, I'm gonna go
find the Samezuka seats.
Haru's here!
Wow, really?
[KISUMI, ASAHI]
Haru!
No way. The guy who
was riding Chappy!
I can't believe you made it!
Sorry that I'm late.
Rei!
[gasps]
[laughs] This'll be my
first time seeing him swim!
Good luck, Rei.
[REI] It's clear now. All I
have to do is be myself!
All right!
For my very last race
in high school,
I'll show you the most perfect
butterfly that I can muster!
[ANNOUNCER 11B]
Take your marks.
--[beep]
--[CROWD] Go!
Go, Rei!
All right!
Come on!
It's all you!
[AYUMU, SHIZURU, ROMIO]
Captain Rei!
[IWATOBI SCHOOL]
Let's go! Let's go, let's go,
let's go, let's go, Rei!
[IWATOBI SCHOOL]
Push it! Push it, push it,
push it, push it, Rei!
Let's go! Let's go, let's go,
let's go, let's go, Rei!
Push it! Push it, push it,
push it, push it, Rei!
[gasps]
[ASAHI] So, he's one
of your guys, huh?
Yeah, I think he'd make a good
rival for you, actually.
Cool.
[ANNOUNCER 11A]
The third heat of the men's
100-meter breaststroke
qualifier is next.
It's almost time for
Ai's breaststroke race!
Yeah.
Go, Ai!
Okay, Nagisa. I won't lose.
Neither will I.
[ANNOUNCER 11B]
Take your marks.
--[beep]
--[CROWD] Go!
Good start!
[MOMOTARO]
He's got an early lead!
Come on, go!
You can do it!
[ROMIO, AYUMU, SHIZURU]
Keep it up!
Nagisa!
[ROMIO] Speed boost!
And right at the end!
Will he make it?
[NITORI]
Nagisa!
Thanks a lot!
Right back atcha!
[HARUKA]
That was awesome.
Really. Great job.
Thanks!
I'm so glad you could be
here to watch the race.
That meant everything to us!
I didn't quite make
it to the finals,
but I beat my
personal best time!
I'm graduating on a good note.
With no regrets!
[MAKOTO]
Nagisa. You've grown a lot.
Thank you. Wow.
I've got so many fun
memories from swimming
with you guys over the years.
I can't even count all of them!
You were always there,
supporting me.
I'll treasure that forever.
Today, too.
The whole time
I was in the water,
it felt like my
heart was dancing.
I just love swimming,
and I'm pretty sure
I always will.
Good.
[SHIZURU]
Romio.
[ROMIO]
Hm?
We have to make it
to the nationals, too.
[ROMIO]
Okay!
One more thing!
We need to commemorate
this day with a photo!
Everybody squeeze in.
Perfect!
Now, let's pose!
[UOZUMI, MINAMI sob]
[UOZUMI]
We gave it our best!
They kinda make me
wanna swim again.
You've been spending
some time in the pool
for rehab, haven't you?
Uh-huh.
I'm nowhere near back to
my full power yet, though.
Well, hurry up and get there
so you can come back.
Oh, I will. But, look.
Try not to cry when I beat you.
Like I would!
[laughs]
[MAKOTO]
Rin!
Wow, I didn't know
you were here, too.
Of course.
Today was the last race
for my old high school team.
[RIN]
Rei and Nagisa swam well, too.
[MAKOTO] Mm-hm. But, are you
sure it was okay to come?
[HARUKA]
It's fine.
Not being here is what
I would've regretted more.
Me, too.
[RIN] I only made it this
far because of the bonds
I have with these guys.
And I'm gonna hold
onto them forever.
Wherever the future takes me!
Haru! You ready?
'Cause it's about
to be our turn.
[HARUKA] Right. It's time
for the All-Japan.
[NAGISA] A battle for
a ticket to the world!
[REI] An opportunity
that only comes once!
[NAGISA]
Next time: "Dive to the Future!"
[REI]
This is the final lap!