[IKUYA]
I'm alone again. I have no one.
No one to save me.
[IKUYA]
So, I guess... I...
[IKUYA gasps, pants]
[phone vibrates]
Good morning, Ikuya.
You sleeping?
[IKUYA] Not anymore,
thanks to you. What's up?
Not much. Thought I'd
give you a wakeup call.
Wouldn't want you to
be late for practice.
[IKUYA]
I'm not gonna be late.
Good, you'd get in trouble.
You know, I've been
thinking about
what happened yesterday.
Your old teammate
from middle school.
Nanase, wasn't it?
Look, it's not that big a deal.
Just forget about it.
I gotta get ready to go,
so, I'll see ya later.
[alarm beeping]
[music plays]
[DAVID]
G'day, Rin.
Oh, hey, David.
So, how do you like
Mikhail as a coach?
He's great, but...
But what?
Quick question, Rin- kun !
Do you like ramen with barbeque
pork or fish cake in it?
He's... different.
[DAVID] He's known for being
smart, but a bit eccentric.
You're lucky though.
Mikhail's really sought after.
He rarely coaches
people one-on-one.
[RIN]
Yeah. I'm kinda surprised.
[DAVID] Well, he must've
seen something in ya
that he likes.
[RIN]
I'm not sure what though.
But regardless, I'm grateful.
Yeah.
Hey, Chris. What's wrong?
Oi! Rin! Guess what?
This random Japanese guy,
just showed up outta nowhere
and asked Mikhail to
coach him! Isn't that crazy?
Huh?
[CHRIS] Mikhail said no,
but then the guy said,
"If I beat everyone here,
then you have to be my coach!"
[DAVID] Japanese guy...
Friend of yours, maybe?
No. Doesn't sound
like anyone I know.
[JOHANN]
He's fast!
[DAVID]
Huh?
[NATSUYA] I'm not that fast--
maybe all of you guys
are just too slow.
Huh?
Well, well, well! Wanna go next?
[RIN]
Sounds fun.
Just try and keep up.
Oh. Somebody's confident!
It isn't worth your time.
[RIN]
But, Coach.
No matter how many
people you can outswim,
I'm still not going
to agree to your deal.
Ugh. Why not?
You've already seen how
easily I beat these guys.
[MIKHAIL] Pure speed is not
the only thing I care about.
[NATSUYA]
So what more do you want?
[MIKHAIL]
If you must know, it's...
[NATSUYA]
Ah-- Uh...
[MIKHAIL]
Muscles.
Huh?
You've got them, but not
really the kind I like.
[NATSUYA]
What does that mean?
He kinda reminds me
of my sister.
You see, Rin- kun 's muscles
are cho-very-good.
Cho-very-what-now?
It's Japanese slang,
it means "amazing."
I figured you would
understand that.
It's not that I
don't understand,
it's that nobody
says that anymore.
Really? Is that true?
Yeah.
Oh, no! I'm uncool!
I'd say I'm MK5, but I
bet that's out, too!
[RIN]
He really is skilled as a coach.
[TSUKAMOTO] Inada got sixth in
the 100-meter breaststroke.
Kiryuu placed third
in 200-meter free.
And Nanase got second
in 100-meter free.
[MIKOSHIBA]
Hey, Nanase.
You okay? You're spacing out.
No, I'm all right.
I'm just thinking.
[TSUKAMOTO] ...focus on those
events during practice.
[IKUYA gasps]
[HOSHIKAWA]
Kirishima.
So, I guess the
tournament went well.
[IKUYA]
Yeah.
You know, your IM
is really amazing.
It's a shame that's your
only event though--
you're such a great swimmer.
Why don't you do
freestyle relay?
Well, that isn't
really my thing.
[HIYORI] Sorry, captain, but
Ikuya doesn't swim in relays.
Why not?
Because he prefers to focus
on the individual events.
Right? Tell him.
Yeah.
I can perform better
if I'm by myself.
[HOSHIKAWA]
What kinda reason is that?
I gotta go. Sorry.
[HOSHIKAWA]
Wasted potential.
[SAOTOME] Hey, do you
wanna go to that meetup
with Oudoukan University later?
Thanks, I would, but I already
have plans for today, so...
[SAOTOME] What, again?
You're no fun, Tachibana.
Sorry, next time.
[SOSUKE]
Kirishima?
Oh. You've been
talking to Nagisa.
[MAKOTO]
Mm-hm.
[SOSUKE]
I think I saw him compete
in the individual medley,
but that's about
all the info I have.
Is there some kind of problem?
[MAKOTO] No. I mean,
Haru talked to him a little.
And from the sound of it...
Well, I dunno, it seems
like he's changed a lot.
[SOSUKE sighs]
[MAKOTO] You know, since Haru
and I both quit swimming
for a while back in middle
school and everything.
Old teammates are tough. Yeah.
Yo.
I guess I haven't introduced
myself to you, have I?
My name's Natsuya Kirishima.
I'm Rin Matsuoka.
[NATSUYA] Really? Thought
Rin was a girl's name.
[NATSUYA sighs]
Uh--
Look, no reason you
gotta be so uptight.
How 'bout we get
somethin' to eat?
This is my first time
here in Sydney.
Come show me around!
Ah!
[RIN]
You like your beer, huh?
[NATSUYA]
Yeah, is that a problem?
[RIN]
Just not sure it's a good idea
for a competitive swimmer.
[NATSUYA]
Well, I don't have a team.
So only person I have
to answer to is me.
Ah. Then what do you...
[NATSUYA]
Collect prize money.
I don't follow.
[NATSUYA] Okay, I spend
my days travelling all over
the world entering races
that offer cash prizes.
Naturally. I win.
And then...
I use the prize money I get
to set off for a new place.
See, there's more than one kind
of lifestyle for swimmers.
A lot of people go this route.
What's wrong?
Uh, nothing.
It does seem like a waste
of your talent, though.
Well, enough about me.
Somebody told me
that you went to Sano.
Uh?
Iwatobi kid here.
Wait, are you kidding?
Then do you know Haru?
Sorry, I mean Haruka Nanase.
Haruka Nanase? Yeah, I know him.
He started going to Iwatobi
when I was in my third year.
You mean middle school, right?
Yeah. Weren't you
at Sano Middle?
Oh, uh, no.
I was here in Australia
as an exchange student
training in swimming.
Damn, you came here
when you were that young?
You were kinda cocky
then, weren't ya?
You think so?
Yeah, maybe a little.
You know, Haruka was
pretty cocky, too.
Always said "I only
swim free." Constantly!
Then again, I heard he
gave up on the sport.
[gasps]
So, what's he been
up to recently?
He's not really done
with swimming, is he?
No. He picked it
back up in high school
and now he's training with
his college team in Japan.
He's aiming for the global
stage, the same as I am.
Swimming with him
at the world level...
That's my dream.
Interesting.
If that's how you feel,
then you might end up
being my little brother's rival.
[RIN]
Oh, you have a brother?
Uh, Natsuya?
[snoring]
[RIN]
Come on, keep it together here.
[NATSUYA]
Sorry, heh.
This is where I'm staying.
Thanks a lot.
What is it?
Nothin'. I stayed at
this place once, too.
[RIN] Jeez, that guy
is so high-maintenance.
[sighs]
Maybe... I'll tell
him in person.
[MAKOTO] Hey, everybody,
sorry I'm so late.
Wait, where's Kisumi?
He said he had a
meeting with his club.
Dang, he's really getting into
this whole college thing, huh?
Yeah, I think it
kinda suits him.
Anyway, do we have a plan
for visiting Ikuya yet?
Actually, you know...
I'm not sure it's a
good idea for all of us
to barge in on him like that.
Maybe, it'd be better
if Kisumi went there solo
and broke the ice first.
What's up? That doesn't
sound like you.
Sorry. I just don't
know what to say,
since I promised him that
I wouldn't move again.
It'll be fine. He's
not mad about that.
That's right, you talked to him
about it before, didn't you?
[MAKOTO]
Mm-hm.
The two of us had a conversation
after you quit the team
and Asahi moved away.
The team broke up, of course,
but it seemed like
he was optimistic
about continuing to swim.
[ASAHI] Hm. Not long after that,
he went off to America
with Natsuya, didn't he?
[MAKOTO]
Yeah.
What was the deal with
that super rude guy
back at the tournament?
Are they friends
from high school?
Dunno.
[ASAHI] I don't even know what
high school Ikuya went to,
or how long he's been
back from the states.
It's kinda like...
even though we all
used to be teammates
when we were younger,
we don't really know
anything about him now.
Hey, good swimming.
But I noticed your rhythm
was a little bit
different than usual.
Is there something on your mind?
[IKUYA]
No, not really.
[HIYORI] You're breathing
kinda heavy, too.
[IKUYA]
You worry too much.
[JOHANN]
He's here again.
That's four days in a row, yeah?
Won't take no for an answer.
Look, mate, you
should prob'ly stop
hangin' out with
this guy every night.
It's not a big deal.
He's harmless.
[RIN]
Mikhail?
[MIKHAIL]
Natsuya- kun .
Come back all you want,
but I won't change my mind.
Heh. Yeah, that's
what you think.
[MIKHAIL]
You're quite confident.
You said you like muscles.
I've got just the thing.
[MIKHAIL]
Mm.
[NATSUYA]
Heh, heh! How's this?
I already have that.
I should've known.
All right, then, how 'bout this?
[gasps]
[NATSUYA]
It's a rare find in Japan,
coveted by muscle
maniacs nation-wide!
I'm pretty sure my little
sister has the same one.
[MIKHAIL]
Does she really?
Well then, please, you must
introduce me to her!
[gasps]
Is everything okay?
I just had a really
ominous feeling.
Ayumu!
If anything should happen
to me, I need you to swear
that you'll protect
this book with your life!
I can't promise you that.
Hey, guys, I'm here.
Look what the cat dragged in.
You could've at least called
and told us you'd be late.
What've you been doing?
Oh, just gathering
some information.
I happened to make friends
with an upperclassman
whose boyfriend is a member
of Shimogami's Swim Club.
For real?
[KISUMI] Mm-hm. And according
to intel collected with my
super detective skills,
the 25th is X Day!
[ASAHI]
X Day?
In other words, it's the one day
they don't have practice.
That's prob'ly the day
you guys should visit Ikuya.
[MAKOTO]
What do you mean "you guys"?
Aren't you going?
[KISUMI]
Me? Sorry, I can't.
I have a meeting with
another club that day--
[ASAHI] Damn it, what's
more important to you?
Your friends or
your stupid clubs?
[KISUMI] They're both important,
don't make me choose!
[NATSUYA] Hate to keep
dragging you out so much.
[RIN] If you feel that bad,
I'll let you buy.
Sorry, can't.
I have a strict policy
against spoiling people.
I guess you're gonna hafta
keep paying for your own food.
[phone vibrates]
[RIN]
Is everything okay?
Message from home.
Ikuya's struggling.
Ikuya?
[NATSUYA]
My little brother.
Why's that ring a bell?
It's Ikuya Kirishima.
Kirishima?
So, Ikuya said he's
having a hard time?
[NATSUYA]
No, that was a friend of his.
They met in America while
he was studying abroad.
That's cool. Your brother went
overseas for swim training, too.
Did you tell me
that you were friends
with Haruka Nanase?
[RIN]
Yeah.
In his first year
of middle school,
Ikuya swam the
relay with Haruka.
But Haruka left the
Swimming Club after that.
[NATSUYA] One by one, his
other teammates either quit
or moved away, so the team
broke up. Ikuya was all alone.
[NATSUYA] That's why,
during his second year,
he came to America,
where I was studying.
I mean, it's not like
I hold it against anybody,
of course.
Once he made it to the states,
he put all of his energy
into practicing with me.
But my brother's problem
is that he gets
so focused on something, he
loses sight of everything else.
One day, he pushed
himself too hard
and almost drowned in the pool.
[NATSUYA] There was no
serious physical damage,
but the mental shock must've
taken a huge toll on him.
He had to stay in the
hospital for a while.
[NATSUYA] Still, I think that
experience made him stronger.
Not just in breaststroke,
but free, butterfly,
and backstroke, too.
He mastered all of them
and completely swore
off doing relays.
He keeps posting better
and better IM times,
but at the pace he's
going, I'm worried
that he might hit a plateau.
I want Ikuya to make it
to the global level.
[RIN]
What about you, though?
Huh?
Don't you wanna get
to that point yourself?
Nah, I don't really need to.
I swim when I want, how I want.
[RIN] Then why did you ask
Mikhail to coach you?
[NATSUYA]
So I can get better, of course.
But, it's not because
I care about medals.
[gasps]
Natsuya, are you saying
your dream is to--
Hey. You feel like
havin' a race with me?
Huh?
Two-hundred-meter freestyle!
What, are you chicken?
[RIN] No, you said you
only swim how you want.
[NATSUYA]
Well, this is what I want!
[RIN]
But, there's no money in it.
[NATSUYA]
Then let's just make a bet.
Uh. Loser buys dinner.
[RIN]
That's not an equal bet, though.
Not the way you drink.
[NATSUYA]
Okay, how 'bout a new swimsuit?
[RIN]
I don't need one right now.
No dice, huh? Let me see.
[RIN laughs]
You're like Sosuke.
[NATSUYA]
Hm?
Oh, Sosuke was a
good friend of mine
from back home.
He always wanted to make
everything a competition.
But, what? He's not
your friend anymore?
[panting]
[RIN]
He's a rival and a friend.
[NATSUYA]
So he's a swimmer like us, then.
[RIN]
Yeah, but he hurt his shoulder.
Once it heals,
I swear we're gonna
swim together again!
And Haruka?
Wow, that seems to be
a common theme with you.
How many of these
dreams do you have?
[NATSUYA]
Mm! Okay, how 'bout this idea?
If I win, then I get to
crash at your apartment!
I only have the hotel
till next week.
[RIN]
Uh...
[chuckles]
[beeping]
[VOICE 3A]
Take your marks!
[beep]
[NATSUYA] Leaning on that
precious leg strength, huh?
Nice try!
[RIN]
He caught up!
[NATSUYA]
Now it's about to get fun!
[RIN]
Damn, he's powerful!
Ha!
Aw!
[NATSUYA]
This sucks.
It wasn't supposed
to storm until tomorrow!
Oh, well, guess there's
always next time.
Do you still need
a place to stay, though?
Think I'll go to Japan.
[RIN]
Huh?
Nice meeting you, Rin.
And thanks, by the way.
Because of you, I remembered
that I have somebody
I wanna swim with, too.
[MIKHAIL] Well, looks like
he got the message.
Did you really not
wanna work with him
because of his muscles?
[MIKHAIL]
Rin- kun .
There are two types of
muscles in this world.
There's the kind of
muscles that I like
and the kind I can do without.
His were the latter.
[RIN]
So you did mean it.
I never say anything
I don't mean.
But still.
I don't feel like there
would have been any point
in my coaching that young man.
[RIN]
Huh?
[MIKHAIL] His face told me
that what matters most to him
is not here.
You figured that out
just from his face?
Of course.
I used to know someone
like that, too.
[REI] At last, our friends
are infiltrating Shimo U!
[NAGISA]
Then what happens?
[REI] Next time:
"Interference of Loss!"
[NAGISA]
A fireworks display of feelings!