[NON giggles]
[yells]
[NON screaming]
[ATSUKO]
Why?
[bell ringing]
Talk about déjà vu.
No joke.
[MIKU] And that's the race!
The winner is Non Toyoguchi.
[chuckles]
[MIKU] Next, Nozomi Kaminashi
will race Usagi Tsukishita.
Sweet, I'm ready to do this!
Do your best out there
and you're sure to win.
I got no clue what I did
to make her hate me so much.
I'm dying to see
what that turnip pulling
training's done for you, Nozomi.
Yeah, you and me both.
Guess my hint came in handy
since you figured it out.
It did! I gotta
thank you 'cause I--
Usagi, I'm sure you've
learned a few tricks
during this training
camp too, right?
Show me your stuff!
Okay, sure.
Anything for you.
Are you obsessed with her?
[USAGI] Why is that
a bad thing? I'm not crazy.
I just really look up
to her, that's all.
In my opinion,
Kusakai's a goddess.
A goddess?
[USAGI] I had to race against
her in the entrance exams
and she kicked my butt.
I was no match for her.
But then, that's when I realized
she's like the goddess Athena.
She's the person I aspire to be!
Her very existence is my oasis
in the desert of life!
[USAGI]
Aaaah! My goddess, Kusakai!
Damn, she's really spillin'
her heart out, ain't she?
One thing's for sure,
Mio. You're loved.
[USAGI]
I had her undivided attention
until you moved up to elite.
You're not even that
great of a Keijo player,
but she's always
got her eye on you.
Not to mention her hands!
[growls]
Lemme guess, that's why
you don't like me?
Damn straight! I'm gonna
show her you have nothing on me!
Only I'm worthy
of her adoration!
It's not like I asked
for her adoration, you know.
But whatever.
If you wanna race,
I'll give ya a good one!
Then bring it on!
You're about to lose big time!
She's fast!
Ugh! She dodged me!
You can't beat me,
'cause I'm fighting to
fulfill my purpose in life.
I want my goddess to
fawn over me instead of you!
Spinning Rabbit Hip!
[yells]
C'mon! Just quit movin'!
Heh. Your butt is so big
and your attacks are so slow,
there's no way
you'll ever touch me.
I'd watch what I say
if I were you.
I learned a few tricks
at this training camp
that just might prove you wrong.
You can do it, Kaminashi.
Show the girls what you learned
in that turnip field.
[USAGI laughing]
[NOZOMI grunts]
[USAGI] It's pointless.
A big butt like yours
will never be fast
enough to hit me!
Butt Flash time.
[USAGI gasps]
That was quick!
Whoa, she did it!
That was just a lucky hit! Uh!
Here's the thing,
I'm a friendly gal
until you start pissin' me off.
My butt may be big
but it's fast, too!
What's up with these attacks?
I thought she was slow!
[NOZOMI grunting]
I guess I might've
underestimated you a little bit.
But still,
that doesn't explain...
...all the attention...
...she gives you!
[groans]
How'd Usagi do that crazy move?
I dunno. Somehow she
changed course midair,
but Nozomi wasn't pulled along.
Now I get it. You're using
your size against me.
Took ya long enough
to figure it out.
But now you know my petite size
is my greatest physical asset.
What is that supposed to mean?
Simple. She's a
small girl, right?
In a confined space,
like a Land,
being small and light on
your feet can prove useful.
It makes it easier to dodge
and regain balance.
And the smaller the target,
the harder it is to hit.
We'll have to wait and see.
Nozomi's not goin'
down without a fight.
There you go, Kaminashi.
You need to take
your butt to the limit.
[USAGI giggles]
No way!
[NOZOMI]
Aw, yeah! I've got you now!
She hit!
No, she only grazed her.
I'm way too close to the edge!
Oh, no you don't!
[NOZOMI] I've finally
got you on the ropes!
I'm not lettin' you
get away from me!
Now, down ya go!
[gasps]
--What?
--She dodged it with a backbend!
[USAGI]
When you're as petite as I am,
you can dodge nearly any attack.
What the--? Her ass
stopped right above me.
I'm gonna take
my butt to... the limit!
Meteor Hip!
[gasps]
[bell ringing]
[MIKU] That's the match!
Tsukishita is down.
The winner is Nozomi Kaminashi!
I did it!
That was absolutely amazing!
The Meteor Hip, huh?
Combining the Butt Flash
into another move
was impressive enough,
but to top it off, she gave
the new technique a name.
--[GIRLS gasping]
--[clapping]
That was an excellent race.
Way to go, ladies!
[MIKU chuckles]
Hey, Usagi. The camp wrap
party's just about to start.
Is somethin' wrong?
The race this afternoon.
It was fun.
Uh? What was that?
I didn't hear ya.
Then nevermind.
Aw, c'mon, just say it again.
I said it was fun racing you.
Really? That's the last thing
that I ever thought
I'd hear you say.
I didn't mean it.
The only person
who's fun around here
is my beloved Kusakai.
I'm so glad we're cool.
I was sure you hated me
for a while there.
I look forward
to racin' you again.
My lovelies made up!
Now I can snuggle both of you!
--[NOZOMI laughing]
--Well... I... uh...
Forget it!
You get away from her!
I'm not gonna
lose to you next time!
I'm happy to see
that she's finally starting
to care about her own races.
And it's all thanks
to you, Nozomi.
[laughs]
[indistinctive chattering]
[clap, clap]
Listen up, everyone.
I'm afraid that our time here
in Kyoto has come to an end.
Now, when we get back to Awaji,
there's no time to rest
because the East-West War
will be here before you know it.
Let's train hard so we can win!
[NOZOMI]
Mmmm! Man, I can't wait!
It's sneakin' up on us.
I'm excited but
I'm kinda scared.
I mean, the East-West War
is a major event.
It takes place
in Shizuoka, doesn't it?
Yeah. At the
Shimizu Keijo Arena--
the largest in the country.
What's crazy is it nearly
sells out every year.
And we're the away team,
so that crowd
is gonna boo us bad.
Just thinking about it
makes my heart race.
It's exhilarating, y'know?
What if all of the hot guys
there end up falling for us?
Ah! I can't handle it!
[GIRLS chattering]
I have a good feeling
this will be our year.
I certainly hope so.
[sighs]
Hey, check it out, Miyata.
You can see
Mount Fuji from here!
[gasps] So, this is
the Shimizu Keijo Arena!
I never imagined I'd
get the chance to compete
in a big stadium like this!
Great. Now I'm scared.
Don't be scared, Aoba.
This is gonna be awesome.
This is our chance to show
the Easterners who's boss.
[KAZANE] Who're they?
Are those Suruga students?
[NON]
Yeah and they look strong.
They've got nicer grounds
and better equipment than we do.
Yeah, no kiddin'. Why do
they get to practice here
while we're stuck
in the crummy area?
Aw, man! It looks
like they even train
with personal coaches.
[HANABI] And they have a drink
station! They're so lucky.
[ATSUKO] They must have
some serious sponsors.
Well, that's one thing the East
has on us: loads of cash.
This blows.
That just ain't fair!
[MIKU] Now, now,
that's enough, ladies!
A fancy practice area,
sponsorships, and media
attention are nice but
they're not necessary to win.
You know what is? Training!
So stop whining
and get back to it!
[ALL groan]
Come on, you want
to win, don't you?
--Then give it your all!
--[ALL] Yes, ma'am.
[AYAKO] The East-West War
is nothing but a joke.
Personally, I think it's time
we put an end to this farce.
[MALE REPORTER 8A]
Would you care to explain?
[AYAKO] In my opinion,
there's no need
for two Keijo training schools;
the West should be
merged with the East.
Setouchi has produced a lot of
mediocre talent who have,
quite honestly,
ruined this wonderful sport.
We know that most of the top
tier players come from the East,
but don't you think you're being
a little too hard on Setouchi?
[AYAKO] Not at all, the results
of the East-West War
have been the same
for the last decade.
Suruga has won the event
every single year.
Setouchi has never
defeated our talent.
What? We've never won?
Is that true?
If we were losing every year
I'd stop competing.
I mean, why put your students
through the heartbreak?
I can't believe
Setouchi's never won.
I know, me either.
You may be in for a surprise
because the players
from the West
are pretty good this year.
Shut up. Don't run
your mouth, moron!
[chuckles] I'm sure
they have some good talent.
However, those girls will never
reach their full potential
at that school.
And that's because
of the teachers.
It's been proven
time and time again
that weak teachers
only produce weak students.
[grunts]
I implore the Keijo
committee to make
a swift decision
regarding this matter.
[clanging]
I was tryin' to ignore ya,
but I couldn't anymore.
Why do you hate
Setouchi so much, lady?
Oh hey, Kaminashi!
I haven't seen you in a while!
--How's it go--
--Think before you speak!
Girls, what're you
doing over there?
Get back here!
You're Setouchi students?
[MIO] You insulted our teachers.
We can't let that slide.
Can't you read? The sign says,
"No outsiders allowed."
[NOZOMI] You think
some sign's gonna stop us?
Our teachers
are wonderful women
who care about their
students and their careers.
Better take back what you said.
She's right; take it back!
[MAYA]
That's enough. I'm warning you,
if you don't leave
our instructor alone
you're in trouble. Got it?
[NOZOMI] Who in the heck is this
girl? A player from the East?
[MAYA] She has the right
to speak her mind without
you and your friends
harassing her.
Go back to your training area.
But first, I suggest
you apologize to her
for trespassing...
...and being disrespect-able!
I don't think...
that's the right word.
[SAYAKA] Perhaps she meant
to say "disrespectful"?
You're who's
bein' disrespectable!
More like a disrespectincompoop!
Anyway, she needs to take back
what she said right now!
[MAYA] Did you not
hear me the first time?
I told you to back off.
[NOZOMI groans]
[NOZOMI] How'd she throw me
back with that tiny body?
She didn't even need to wind up!
What's the deal with this girl?
I believe that
I've made myself clear.
If I were you, I would leave
before I get seriously hurt.
If you continue to harass--
Watch it.
Don't underestimate us.
Setouchi'll thrash ya!
Well, that was an interesting
technique you used.
You wouldn't mind showing it
to me again, would you?
Yeah, like that's gonna happen.
[NOZOMI] My body's so numb
after that, I can't move.
A Sandstorm?
You better not
touch Nozomi again.
Otherwise, this tiny
spat'll turn into a brawl.
[KAHO] You think
this is a "tiny spat"?
Well, this is already
a brawl, if you ask me.
How cute! Twins who
use their butts together!
Oh, now you've done it!
Mess with my beloved
and you'll feel my wrath!
Back off! In case you forgot,
you guys started this.
Not very bright.
Keep talking smack to us
and we might just have to
do something about it.
Is that a threat?
I wasn't lookin' for a fight
but I tell ya what, big gal,
if that's what you want,
then I'll give it to ya.
This needs to stop right now!
Ms. Kobayakawa?
[MIKU] I'd like to apologize
on behalf of our students
for the trouble they've caused.
[NOZOMI] But this lady
was trash-talkin' you
and the other teachers
at Setouchi!
If anyone should
apologize it's her!
[ALL gasp]
[AYAKO] Hmph! There's nothing
to see here, ladies.
Time to get back to work.
[AKARI, KAHO, NAMI, SAKI]
Right!
Maya. Come along.
Yes.
[MAYA] Something about
that girl bothers me.
What were you thinking?
You trespassed on
private property to pick
a fight with our opponents?
[NOZOMI] You'd understand
if you'd heard what she said!
It doesn't matter, Kaminashi!
What did you achieve
by confronting her?
Absolutely nothing.
If you want to be top athletes,
you need to learn
to solve problems like adults.
Take them to the Land
and beat them fair and square.
That being said...
We were proud to see you
stand up for us like that.
Thank you, ladies.
We're determined to give you the
best Keijo coaching possible.
Tomorrow I want you
to go out there
and show them
what you've learned!
That'll teach 'em to respect us!
[ALL]
Yes, ma'am!
All right. It's time to go over
the rules of the East-West War.
Things are a little
different this year.
You're going to be competing
in teams of four players.
Each race is five minutes.
The school that's first to win
two races wins the war.
Does anyone have any questions?
We can win two races, right?
Here's hoping we can win
two consecutive races!
It's four-on-four team battles?
This is gonna be awesome.
Listen closely for
your team assignment.
On Team One: Mio Kusakai.
Aw, yeah!
--[HITOMI] Mari Murata.
--[MARI] Wha--?
[HITOMI] Kotone Fujisaki
and Sayaka Miyata.
Team One it is, then.
On Team Two: Atsuko Yoshida.
Usagi Tsukishita.
Kazane Aoba. Non Toyoguchi.
Aw, why do they keep stickin'
me with the hard heiney lady?
Please don't start
calling me that.
My name's Yoshida, okay?
[HITOMI] On Team Three:
Rin Rokudou. Saya Kogatana.
Hanabi Kawai. Nozomi Kaminashi.
Guess we're the anchor, huh?
Yay! I'm glad we're
on the same team!
Those Suruga chicks
aren't ready for this!
They're gonna regret
picking on us!
--[KOTONE] Mm!
--[ALL] Yeah!
This place is foul.
Why's Sayaka competing here?
What a waste of time.
I'm going home.
Oh, no you don't.
You've come this far,
there's no going back.
Now let's go, dear.
[ANNOUNCER 8A]
Ladies and gentlemen,
it's time for the spectacular
battle royale featuring
the future stars of Keijo.
The East-West War!
This is our eleventh
annual event to determine
who will rise to the top:
the East or the West!
Who will the goddess of victory
smile upon this year?
That's weird.
Did ya see the line-up?
Yeah! Miss Kaminashi's
in the third race.
I can't wait to see her in ac--
No, not that! The East's
best player's missing.
She's not on here.
That seems odd to me.
Yeah, you're right!
Do they think
the West isn't worthy
of competing against
their best player? Ugh!
Man, they're really
down on Setouchi.
[NOZOMI] Oooh!
You guys look amazin'!
If your father
saw you in this outfit,
I bet he'd totally
understand your decision.
Actually, I think it would
have the opposite effect.
He couldn't care less
about the East-West War.
Aw, c'mon, you don't know that!
He could secretly be watchin'.
[NAGISA]
Okay everyone, listen up.
The East-West War is upon us.
You're more than
Setouchi trainees,
you're future pros that will
someday represent the West.
This is your chance
to show the world
the skills you've
worked so hard for.
We're proud of you, girls.
Now go out there
and give 'em a good fight!
[ALL]
Right!
We have a ten year
winning streak
and it's our duty
to keep it going.
The Setouchi trainees
have no idea what it's like
to race against qualified
players like yourselves.
Which means that we'll simply
have to teach
the poor fools a lesson.
There's no need
to be compassionate.
They need to learn that the
world of Keijo is unforgiving.
[ALL]
Right!
[CROWD cheering]
[ANNOUNCER 8A] It's almost time
for the first race.
The players are making
their way to the Land!
First up, from Suruga,
let's hear it for
Saki "The Ogre" Hanayama!
Also from Suruga, we have
Kaho and Akari Fuyuzora!
These two young ladies
are a special treat
because we rarely see
twins in Keijo!
And rounding out Suruga's
team is Nami Nanase,
otherwise known as
"Ass-Eater Nanase"!
Shabam!
[ANNOUNCER 8A] Next up,
we have Setouchi's team:
Mio Kusakai, Kotone Fujisaki,
Mari Murata, and Sayaka Miyata.
All right, ladies and
gentlemen, it's show time!
What's with the
short introduction?
That doesn't seem very fair.
[ANNOUNCER 8A] The first race
of the day will take place
on a junglegym style Land!
It's constructed of
synthetic resin pipes
that become slippery when wet.
This one's gonna be
tough on the outfighters!
The regulars here
at Shimizu Keijo Arena
are very familiar
with this Land.
The question is, how will these
budding young athletes
handle it?
[NAMI giggles]
And what are you giggling about?
Who are you again? Nyanyase?
Nanase! I'm giggling
because I'm happy!
I can't help but smile
'cause it's not every day
that I get to take down
a famous judo player.
Huh?
Like it or not, you're
gonna be my stepping stone
to stardom. I'm goin' big time!
Are you serious?
Yeah. My dream is
to become a Keijo idol.
I wanna sing while I fight!
I'm currently preparing
for my debut race.
My, my, I'm impressed
that you can sing
and fight at the same time.
I'll bet you've got a lovely
singing voice, don't cha?
Hey, I've always wanted a little
songbird to keep me company.
How 'bout you join me
in bed tonight?
I'd love a private show.
There's no way in hell
I'm doing that!
What's with you?
You always this weird?
[ALL]
Yeah, pretty much.
Take a good look at yourself.
You take the cake on weirdness.
Keijo doesn't
need idols, Nyonyose.
It's Nanase, dummy!
And if I were you,
I'd shut my fat mouth.
It's not like anyone wants
career advice from you.
Why? It sounds like
you could use it.
Because you're in
no place to give advice.
You had a judo career
and you ditched it.
You just ran away.
No, that's not true.
[ANNOUNCER 8A] The race
will begin in thirty seconds.
Ladies, take your places.
[ANNOUNCER 8A] This is it,
folks! Their clothes are off!
Both teams are ready!
The East-West War starts now!
This doesn't seem right.
I'm not sure I can watch.
[CROWD cheering]
C'mon, Miyata!
You've got this!
[ANNOUNCER 8A]
Five seconds.
Four. Three. Two. One.
I'm coming for you!
[gasps] Why'd she change
her stance like that?
[SAYAKA yells]
[NAMI]
Her nips are beaming!
[NOZOMI] Next time:
"Ruler of the Jungle Gym!!!!"