[NARRATOR] In the past,
gamblers have been limited
to horse, bike, boat,
and car races,
but now there's a new form
of legalized gambling
sweeping the nation.
It's called Keijo!
Players compete to be
the last girl standing
atop a floating platform
called a "Land."
The kicker? They can only
use their boobs and butts!
The question is:
Who will rule the Land?
Will it be the 18-year-old
Nozomi Kaminashi?
She's one of the
many young ladies
whose search for fame
and fortune has lead them
to the world of Keijo!
And this is the story of their
journey to becoming champions!
Take this!
[gasps]
[ALL gasp]
[ALL scream]
No way.
Whoa. What happened?
But how did she?
[NON screams]
Hey, Nozomin! What
has gotten into you?
[NOZOMI]
My hips hurt... real bad.
[HITOMI]
Medics!
[NOZOMI groaning]
[NOZOMI]
Why does it hurt so much?
[NON]
Nozomin!
Are you okay?
Don't worry. I'm gonna be fine.
[chuckles]
The way that she
twisted her hips.
Impossible.
She's only been at Setouchi
for a couple of months.
She couldn't pull it off.
You'd think. But there's
no denying what we saw.
[NON] I hope Nozomin's not
seriously hurt or anything.
Me too.
I'm kinda worried since she
didn't make it back to class.
[NOZOMI groaning]
[NOZOMI]
Aw, man, that feels so good!
I can't thank you
enough, Kazane.
[NON]
You're back!
Yep, and I feel a lot better
after gettin' that
amazin' massage.
That's good to hear!
So what'd I miss in
the lecture today?
We learned about the
different classifications
of Keijo players.
[NOZOMI]
Okay...
They fall into one
of three categories
based on their fighting style.
What three categories?
[SAYAKA]
First, there's the "infighter,"
who excels at close
range attacks
and relies on pure strength.
[NOZOMI]
Interesting.
[SAYAKA] Second,
there's the "outfighter,"
who likes to keep their distance
and uses speed to strike.
[NOZOMI]
Makes sense.
[SAYAKA]
And the third is the "counter."
They use their opponent's
attacks and strength
against them in order
to secure a win.
[NOZOMI]
Oh, wow.
If that's the case,
I guess you'd be considered
an outfighter, huh?
I mean, you're pretty fast.
Most likely.
I'm usually much quicker
than my opponent
so that may be the
best tactic for me.
Should be the perfect
fit for... my butt attacks.
Most def! That Butt
Gatling you did was crazy!
It would've knocked out
anybody other than Ms. Ujibe.
I've never seen
someone move so fast.
I've always been
proud of my speed.
It was one of my
strengths in Judo.
I believe it. You never stay
in one place for very long.
Talk about an annoyin' opponent.
What did you just call me?
Now, now, calm down.
Here's an idea.
Let's hurry and get dressed
so we can go pick up
our brand new swimsuits!
That reminds me. Thanks
for ruining our old ones.
Huh? You can't
blame me for that!
You guys prob'ly popped 'em
'cause you gained a ton
of weight or somethin'!
Yeah.
Like we're going
to put on weight
when we're in physical
training all day, every day.
[NOZOMI]
How else would you explain it?
[HANABI] You used the air
to slice through them.
[NOZOMI]
Oh, hey! What's with the robes?
One of the elite class
perks are spa treatments.
No fair!
It's amazing what the
spa does for your skin.
Here, let me show you.
Touch my neck. You won't believe
how soft and smooth it feels.
No thanks. I 'm good.
Cut it out, Kusakai.
You're making
Nozomi uncomfortable.
Fine!
I heard that you were taken
to the infirmary today.
So are you feeling all right?
Yeah, Kazane just gave me
an exhilarating massage.
I'm back to full strength.
Oh, wow, really?
Massage is awesome, but
pressure points can help, too.
Yeah?
[HANABI]
Definitely. Let me show you.
[screams]
Holy moley!
Whoa! My body feels lighter!
For real! That worked wonders!
Uh. Hey, Kawai.
What were you
talking about before?
[HANABI] Oh, yeah! I know why
your swimsuits ripped apart.
It was a Vacuum
Butt Cannon, right?
I don't know what
you're saying.
So you did it without
even knowing what it was?
It's a Keijo technique
that combines
powerful rotational energy
and a sharp twist of the hips.
It allows the player to
slash through the air.
[NOZOMI] Gee, I didn't
know I had it in me.
It's such a difficult move
that there are pro players
who've never been
able to master it.
Using your butt to
rip through the air...
The Vacuum Butt
Cannon's a big deal.
Anyone who mastered the move
has become a prize queen.
[NOZOMI]
A prize queen? Oh yeah!
I could move into a fancy
high-rise, drive a luxury car,
and eat like a friggin' king!
I've made up my mind!
I'm gonna make it
my signature move!
If you ask me, you're way too
talented for the regular class.
[ALL]
Huh?
Hello, ladies. I'm the fastest
outfighter in Western Japan.
Rin Rokudo.
Nice to meet ya.
I seriously doubt that you're
the fastest, but whatever.
[HANABI] Miss Rokudo's in
the elite class with us.
Yeah, and she's a weird one.
She's kinda full of herself.
Cute though. She reminds
me of a little kitten.
That's why I've
nicknamed her Rin-rin.
Uh! Hey, I told you to
stop calling me that!
Rin-rin, you said that you
were an outfighter, right?
[RIN] Ugh, please do not
use that stupid nickname.
If you're the fastest
in Western Japan,
let's see what you've got.
[chuckles]
[RIN]
Okay, try and count my attacks.
Well? How many did you count?
I'd go ahead and round up.
[NOZOMI] She's so fast,
I couldn't even see them.
And the answer is--
[NOZOMI]
She disappeared!
[NON screams]
A total of 30 thrusts.
How'd she get over
there so quickly?
I dunno.
Now do you believe
that I'm the fastest?
Rin-rin. It's no fair. Why do
you always hog all the fun?
When it comes to speed,
nobody can match me.
I leave 'em all behind.
[NON screaming]
Oops! My bad!
[HANABI] Now you've don't it,
Rin-rin! You've gone too far!
Y'know, you're wasting
your time, Kaminashi.
You'd be better off training
with the elite class.
What?
Let's be real, you've got
serious Keijo potential.
But you're not gonna grow
as long as you're training
with your weak roommates.
Who're you calling "weak"?
Hey now, our class has
some pretty good players.
We do.
But you're the only decent
fighter in the regular class.
The others are lame and none
of them even come close
to being in my league
as an outfighter.
You might as well train
with your new BFFs.
You know you're gonna
ditch these losers
and join us in elite.
What're you talking about?
[RIN]
Wait. You haven't heard?
There's an event coming that's
going to shake things up.
It'll be fun for us, but maybe
not so much for your roommates.
An event, huh?
[RIN]
Yep, the class-change race.
It's time for us to get
back to our rooms, ladies.
Take care! See you soon, Nozomi!
[MIO]
Quit pushing!
Wow.
I can't decide whether
she's confident or arrogant.
I'd say both.
I dunno how I feel about
a "class-change race."
I'm happy to stay
where I am now.
What do you think, Miyata?
I think you're lucky.
You've got members
of the elite class
practically begging you
to train with them.
Why is she upset?
So she thinks she's
the fastest outfighter?
[HITOMI] Next up,
Momo Horiuchi. Outfighter.
[MOMO]
Right!
[HITOMI] And last but
not least, room 309.
Miyata: Outfighter.
Toyoguchi: Counter.
Aoba: Outfighter.
[SAYAKA, NON, KAZANE]
Right!
[HITOMI]
Kaminashi.
Yes, ma'am?
I cannot assign you yet.
Ms. Ujibe would like to
have a word with you.
Please head to the staff room.
Tell me.
Have you ever heard
of a Keijo technique
called the Vacuum Butt Cannon?
Uh, well yeah.
I've been told that's the move
I accidentally used against
you during the mock race.
I see. Guess word
travels fast.
That fact that you could
pull it off is impressive.
Even if it was by sheer luck.
It'd be a powerful weapon
if you mastered it.
One that could propel you
to Keijo superstardom.
You really think so?
[NAGISA]
I know so.
Every woman who's mastered that
technique and used it in races
has gone on to become
a prize queen.
Oh, yeah! Show me the money!
[NAGISA]
Kaminashi.
Listen. I forbid you from
using that technique again.
Do wha--?
[NAGISA]
Did you hear what I just said?
Well, yeah. I heard the part
about becoming a prize queen.
I said I forbid you from
using that technique!
But I don't understand.
If it could launch my Keijo
career, then why can't I use it?
There's too much risk involved.
I want our students to have
long and healthy careers.
But that move could
make me a prize queen.
[NAGISA] You know what happened
to the women who used it?
They damaged their hips
and were forced into
an early retirement.
The technique
requires the player
to create rotational energy
by violently spinning
and then swinging
their hips like a whip.
When performed,
it puts incredible strain
on the hips and
surrounding joints.
Most professional
players avoid it
'cause they're afraid
of hurting themselves.
And you're still a novice.
If you're not careful, you could
irreparably damage your hips,
then you'll never
be able to go pro.
One false move and
your career's over.
Okay, but still--!
[NAGISA]
I'm warning you.
If you insist on trying
to master this technique,
you'll be expelled
from Setouchi.
[NOZOMI gasps]
Conversation's over.
[NOZOMI]
Wait! Hear me out first!
[NAGISA]
I'm listening.
I didn't decide to
come to Setouchi
just so I could get
enough training to go pro.
If I'm gonna play Keijo,
then I wanna be the best at it.
And I wanna win!
I don't ever wanna go through
the pain of losin' again.
If I can master a technique,
one that makes me a prize queen,
then I'm gonna!
I like it here. I'm learnin'
all sorts of stuff.
But I wanna at least
give it a shot!
At this school, we take pride
in training Keijo players.
We're not going to
allow our students
to needlessly risk
their careers.
I understand that.
And I know I risk
hurting myself,
but that'll just make
me practice more!
[NOZOMI]
I'm begging you.
Teach me the Vacuum Butt Cannon.
What is it about that technique?
You do realize there
are plenty of others
that don't come with the risk.
I wanna learn the
Vacuum Butt Cannon
'cause I know it'll
make me a prize queen.
Sometimes knowing when to give
up is the strongest move of all.
Look, I get what
you're sayin'...
...but there's no way
I'm gonna give up,
not when there's so
much on the line!
I hafta prove myself!
Very well then.
I'll help you master
the technique,
but you're not gonna like it.
I want you to wear this
suit every day for a month.
Whoa, that's weird lookin'.
Is it cosplay?
Don't mock my training.
Okay. So I seriously
have to wear this?
If you wanna learn
the Vacuum Butt Cannon.
Are you giving up before
we even get started?
No, I'll wear it!
[NON]
Nozomin!
Why are you wearing
that crazy get up?
[NOZOMI]
I-It's pulling on my body.
If I let my guard down....
[NOZOMI yelping]
[NOZOMI screams]
Oh my. It kinda looks
like a racing suit.
It's called a UTM.
And what does that stand for?
It's Ujibe's Training Maillot.
You look dumb.
Hey, don't say that!
I already know, okay!
Man, this sucks!
But I'm not gonna let
it get the best of me.
[screams]
[HANA]
What's with the unitard?
[HARUMI] Rumor has it
she pissed off Ms. Ujibe,
and wearing that's
her punishment.
[screams]
[HARUMI] Ugh. Looks like
a pain in the butt.
[HANA] Yeah, I kinda
feel bad for her.
It's hard to even
walk in this suit.
How'm I supposed to get
anything done like this?
It's pullin' against me.
Gotta tense my muscles
or I'm done for!
I can barely move...
[NOZOMI screams]
Nozomin!
I can't swim in this thing?!
What the heck? A swimsuit
that makes you drown?
Now I've seen everything.
Bet this is some kinda test.
I'm gonna pass
with flyin' colors
and make the Vacuum
Butt Cannon mine!
[HITOMI] Move it, Kaminashi,
you're in the way!
If you wanna train,
do it poolside!
[NOZOMI] Sorry!
I'm too slow.
I've gotta move faster.
[NOZOMI groaning]
[yelps]
[NON]
Ooh!
[NOZOMI]
Ah! That was my fried chicken!
[grunting]
[groans]
[NOZOMI grunting]
This is hard, but there's
no way that I'm givin' up!
I'll make the Vacuum Butt
Cannon my signature move!
[SAYAKA] It's still not
enough. I need to go faster.
I won't lose to her!
Aoba, why are you
reaching for her butt?
[KAZANE yelping]
Oh, wow! Really?
That sounds amazing!
In that case, I'll help you
touch as many butts as possible!
If you've got sore
muscles from training,
then come get a
massage from Aoba!
You'll love it, trust me!
Wait, so what's going on here?
[NON]
Would you like a massage?
She's a great masseuse.
And the best part about it
is it's free of charge!
[YUKO] Oh wow,
you've got magic fingers!
[NON] Okay, everyone, line up
and we'll be with you shortly.
[GIRL B sighs]
[GIRL B] Oh, yeah. This is
exactly what I needed.
[NON]
If you like your massage,
be sure to tell
all your friends!
See? Now you'll be able
to get data on everybody!
[GIRL B] I can't get over
how good this feels!
It feels like my entire
body's being compressed.
And it makes my
training much harder.
Ugh! This rubber's too tight.
If it's that uncomfortable
then tell Ms. Ujibe.
[NOZOMI]
And admit defeat?
No, I can handle it,
but I could move faster if it
covered a smaller surface area.
[SAYAKA]
Smaller surface area? Faster?
That's it!
[NOZOMI groans]
Kaminashi. You're too tense.
Try to loosen up.
Easier said than done
when you do what I'm doing.
But If your muscles
are all tensed up,
they're not gonna work
as well as they should.
You need to learn to relax them.
Guess it couldn't hurt to try.
[NOZOMI inhaling, exhaling]
[NOZOMI]
That's the trick!
When I relax, it makes
my whole body flexible
and I can move with
no problem at all!
I finally figured it out!
Still not enough.
[yells]
This'll work. I know it will.
What the heck? Ugh!
The suit feels like it's even
tighter than it was before.
Sheesh!
[NON]
Nozomin! Nozomin!
Yeah, what's up?
The teachers just
put up the info
about the
class-change race!
Oh, really?
So the time has come.
I can't wait for them to see
how strong my butt is now!
[NAGISA]
It's been three months
since you ladies first
joined Setouchi's ranks.
You've trained hard and
studied form and technique
in order to improve the strength
and agility of your butts.
I'm sure you're wondering
if you've become stronger.
Well, today we're
going to find out
as you compete in your
first class-change race.
I hope you aren't too attached
to your current classes.
I've got a feeling this race
is gonna switch things up!
[NOZOMI] Why'd they put an elite
class member in each group?
[SAYAKA]
Because that's how you advance.
Someone from the regular
class can't move up
unless they defeat an elite.
[NOZOMI] Kotone Fujisaki. I've
never seen her fight before.
[RIN]
Aw, man, what a bummer!
I was hopin' I'd get
to race against you.
There's no one else
in the regular class
who can keep up with me.
This is gonna be way too easy.
[NOZOMI]
We've got some amazin' players!
Yeah. Whatever you say.
But even if you did,
they wouldn't stand
a chance against me.
Gimme a break, that's
not true. There's plenty--
[MIKU]
Competitors in the first race,
please make your
way to the front.
Guess it's time for me to go.
[NOZOMI]
Hey, wait!
I was talking to--
Man, she doesn't listen
to anyone, does she?
Uh?
Miyata...
[NAGISA]
Let's go over the rules.
You'll be competing against
three other students
and the race will
last five minutes.
As usual, the last person
standing on the Land
is the winner.
You'll draw to determine which
kind of Land you'll be using.
Who wants to do
the honors, ladies?
[MIKU] The first group will
compete on a Seesaw-Style Land.
[SAYAKA]
Oh, boy.
[MIKU] The race will
begin in five minutes.
[NOZOMI]
It doesn't look any different
than a Basic Land to me.
Ya think it's got a special
trick to it or somethin'?
[SAYAKA]
I don't know.
But I'll find out soon enough.
[NOZOMI]
I'm sorry about before.
I should've told Rin
how good you are.
Guess I just wasn't thinkin'.
No big deal. I'll surprise her.
Yeah, there ya go!
You've got this one in
the bag, Miyata, trust me!
[chuckles]
Win it! I know you can!
I've got this.
[MIKU]
Five seconds to start.
Four. Three. Two. One.
[RIN]
This'll be easy.
Huh?
[SAYAKA]
You're going down!
'Kay, Three. Two. One.
What the hell?
W-Acceleration. Activate!
[NOZOMI] Next time: "The Battle
for the Fastest Butt!"