[NOZOMI] It's a big day here
at Setouchi Training School.
We're currently in the middle
of the class-change race.
I'm in the regular
class right now,
but if all goes well, I'm gonna
be movin' up to elite class!
It's time to show 'em how
hard I worked this month.
I'm gonna win this race,
no matter what!
Uh? What's going on?
That's weird. I feel so
much lighter than before.
Hey. This must be
the UTM payin' off.
All right! I've
totally got this!
Watch out, elite class!
I'm comin' for ya!
Leave me alone! I despise you!
Really?
Well, In that case,
I might as well do something
that'll make you hate me more.
[MAN B gasps]
But what're you--?
[MAN A chuckles]
--I can't believe her!
--That's the stuff.
[splash]
[HITOMI]
Group four will be competing
atop a Fountain-Type Land.
The race will begin
in five minutes.
Competitors, please make
your way to the pool.
Guess it's time.
[NOZOMI]
Hey, Fujisaki.
Hope you don't mind,
they let me draw the Land.
I'm excited. I've never been
on a fountain one before.
Yeah? Good for you.
What's up with her?
Is she gonna wear those
headphones throughout the match?
Do ya mind if I ask
what you're listenin' to?
Guess she doesn't think
we're a challenge.
[KOTONE]
Give that back!
I just wanna hear
what you're into!
You're so strong, but I'll
make you weak in the knees.
What in the heck was that?
[NOZOMI] I wonder if
Fujisaki's a strong fighter.
Well, she's gotta
be at least decent.
I mean, she's elite.
You've gotta be kidding me!
Fujisaki's a thoroughbred!
What's that supposed to
mean? Thoroughbred how?
Her mother was a pro Keijo
player back in the day.
Not only that, she was
also a major prize queen.
[NOZOMI]
Seriously?
She's the daughter
of a prize queen?
[HANABI]
Oh, that's nothing.
Her older sister's currently
a pro Keijo player.
She's been surrounded by the
sport ever since she was a kid.
Sounds like she's gonna be
a tough one to beat, Nozomin.
No worries.
Now that I'm out of
that UTM contraption,
I'm in tip top shape.
I've got this in the bag.
[SAYAKA]
Don't be too cocky.
That'll get you into
trouble, you know.
[NON] I'm worried
'cause we have no idea
what kinda techniques
she's gonna try to use.
And we all saw what
happened with Kusakai.
Hey, guys. Speaking of,
where's Kazane?
She's bummed about losing.
Said she needs to be
alone for a while.
I feel bad for her.
Worry about her later.
You've gotta focus on
your race right now.
You're up!
Keep your eyes on
your opponents, okay?
[NOZOMI]
Mhm.
You don't have to tell me!
[NOZOMI] Whoa, this Land's
incredibly slippery.
If I'm not careful
I might fa-- Ah!
Oh no, I'm sorry!
Wow. Guess that's a
thoroughbred for ya.
You weren't even fazed by--
Um.
I wanna be the only
man you care about!
Now you're finally
being honest with me.
Yes.
Huh? What are you lookin' at?
[KOTONE squeals]
[KOTONE]
I know what you heard earlier,
but it's not what
you're thinking!
I swear! I'm totally not into
BL! Not even a little bit!
[NOZOMI]
Okay?
[MIKU] The next race
will start in ten seconds.
[HANABI]
Uh-oh, I completely forgot!
I was supposed to
warn Nozomi. Oopsie.
About what?
[MIKU]
Five seconds...
[HANABI] I wanted to
warn her to watch out
for Fujisaki's Cerberus.
[SAYAKA]
Excuse me?
[MIKU]
Two. One.
What ithe hell?
Why's she keepin'
her back turned?
It's kinda weirdin' me out.
[SHIZUKA] You think this'll be
an easy win, don't ya?!
What?! She dodged and
still got a hit on me?
And she wasn't even
facin' this way!
She could hear you coming!
If you wanna sink her,
you gotta be stealthy!
[yells]
She got me!
[REI screams]
Whoa, she can dodge and
attack without even lookin'.
[KOTONE] I'm dying to find
out what happens next
in Weak-Kneed Boy ,
so I'm gonna wrap this up.
[roaring]
[ALL gasp]
What's gotten into her?
Her butt's chasing me
around the Land!
[HANABI chuckles]
Most Keijo players
have to train hard
to turn their butts into
weapons, but not her.
Cerbie. Fetch.
[CERBERUS growling]
[HANABI] Fujisaki's butt
does all the work for her.
[MIKU] Kimura has gone
overboard. Loser!
[NON]
That's Cerberus?
[SAYAKA]
It's like a hunting dog.
[roars]
"Cerbie"?
The rumors are true.
You can knock your opponents off
with your back turned to 'em.
[KOTONE]
There's only two left.
Let's hurry and finish this.
She noticed!
[NOZOMI]
She's reading my moves.
Aw, crap!
[NOZOMI yelping]
The way that you responded
to my attack just now...
...you're amazin'!
It's almost like your butt's
got a mind of its own!
[NOZOMI] Hey! Why dontcha
turn around and face us?
[MEN laughing]
Yes.
[NOZOMI] I expected more
from a "thoroughbred."
You're just flyin' by
the seat of your pants!
Don't you care about the race?
[KOTONE] If I'm being honest,
I don't care at all.
I don't enjoy playing Keijo.
It's just a job to me.
It is?
[KOTONE]
All I have to do is show up
and Cerbie'll knock my
opponents off the Land.
I don't love it, but if I can
make decent money playing,
then I might as well.
[REI] Huh? What the hell are
you going on and on about?
I get it.
Keijo's not as important to you
as it is to the rest of us here.
You're interested in other
things. What was it again?
B-- B--
[KOTONE] No! I don't know
where you got that idea,
but you're wrong!
I'm not into BL!
Oh, yeah! That's it: BL!
Ugh. What's it even
matter to you anyway?
I'm ready to get
this race over with
so you'll just leave me alone.
[NOZOMI]
Then bring it on!
But I'm tired of
lookin' at your back.
You're gonna have to face me.
Whether you like it or not.
You're never gonna
forget the day
you raced Nozomi Kaminashi.
Just watch, you'll see.
What do you think you're doing?
You can't defeat her
all on your own!
Fujisaki's ass is
basically a homing missile
and we're its targets!
If we wanna sink her,
then we have to work together.
But I like to work alone.
[roaring]
That's enough talk.
It's time I sent you
two overboard.
[NOZOMI screams]
Let's see you try!
That was nuts!
Did you see her counter?
I don't get it. Does she
not have any blind spots?
[KOTONE]
You can run from Cerbie,
but there's nowhere
you can hide.
Not as long as you're
on the Land, anyway.
Damn, you're persistent!
[screams]
[KOTONE] You can see
which way she's gonna fall.
Knock her off, Cerbie.
Nozomi!
Uh! That was close!
Huh? What happened?
She totally missed.
I've never seen her miss before.
[KOTONE]
I need to pay more attention.
If I keep rushing things, then I
won't be able to read her moves.
Wait. Why do I even care?
It's not like me.
I'll just leave everything
to Cerbie as usual.
[gasps]
[splash]
[NOZOMI]
I'm gonna push you off!
[KOTONE]
Get her, Cerbie.
I've got you now. The race
is as good as over.
[gasps]
Obedience class
is now in session!
My "Vibe-Ring Hip"'ll tame ya!
Did you seriously think
you were gonna beat me?
Wow, Nozomi's a genius!
She's using Fujisaki's
own body against her.
How so?
Well, let's just say, she's
sensitive south of the border.
[KOTONE]
What's going on?
She's completely
throwing me off my game!
This has to stop!
I can't take it anymore!
[KOTONE] Forget it!
I won't let you beat me!
This is the first time...
that I've wanted to fight.
I've never wanted to
sink someone so badly.
[chuckles]
Well, you finally
faced me. Let's go!
[HANABI] Fujisaki can feel
even the smallest vibrations
on the Land with
the soles of her feet.
It's how she's able to read
her opponent's moves.
So that's what you meant by
"sensitive south of the border."
Uh-huh.
That's basically the
secret behind Cerberus.
Aha! I knew there had
to be somethin' to it.
Normally, she keeps her back to
her opponents the whole time,
but she can't today.
Nozomi's making this
race difficult for her
by attacking in ways
she can't predict.
That's why Cerberus is off.
[KOTONE] Grab her and throw
her off the Land, Cerbie.
[NOZOMI] What an amazin'
combo! I can't dodge it!
You would think she'd let
Nozomin recover between attacks.
No, she's doing
it intentionally.
That must be Cerberus's
fighting style. Yes.
It reminds me of the way
a hunter and her dog
would work together.
Talk about intense!
[KOTONE]
I'm done playin' games.
Crap!
How'd I miss again?
Barely evaded.
Looks like I'll have to start
gettin' creative with my moves.
She got away.
Let's try it again. Cerbie!
Yay! Way to go, Nozomi.
She's using her gymnastic
skills to avoid Fujisaki.
The UTM sure made her stronger!
There we go.
I'm still here.
But all I'm really doin' is
runnin' from her attacks.
[KOTONE] Oh, come on!
Just fall off already!
I'm over this lame race.
Well, I'm not about to
go down without a fight.
I've got an attack
that'll finish you off.
[NOZOMI]
What's it doin'?
[NOZOMI screams]
[KOTONE gasps]
How the hell is she still
standing? It makes no sense.
[NOZOMI]
I dunno if I'll make it.
If she hits me with that big
attack again, I'm done for.
What now?
I've gotta think. There must
be somethin' I can do.
What is it with you?
Why won't you fall off the land?
Just give up!
[NOZOMI]
There's no way that's happenin'.
'Cause I wanna win!
You may be strong, but I
won't let you defeat me!
[gasps]
[NOZOMI]
I swear, I will... beat you!
The way she's twisting
and spinning...
Here goes.
[NOZOMI]
Take this!
[KOTONE]
That was insane!
Where'd all that
power come from?
Vacuum Butt Cannon.
Man, she dodged.
Guess I'll just have
to try it again.
And this time I won't miss ya!
In that case, let's get
down to business, shall we?
It's time for us to
finish this, Cerbie.
[NOZOMI yells]
They're so fast! It's hard to
tell who's who at this point.
They're both going for
their finishing moves.
I've got you now.
You're goin' down!
I've had enough.
I'm ending this!
[KOTONE, NOZOMI]
Finish her.
Vacuum Butt Cannon!
[KOTONE]
Full-Power Cerberus!
They're even!
Unfortunately for Cerberus,
it can only gain
momentum on the Land.
Meanwhile, the
Vacuum Butt Cannon
gains powerful centrifugal force
thanks to the player's
building rotations.
Fujisaki doesn't stand a chance.
[KOTONE screams]
No way.
[MIKU]
Fujisaki is overboard. Loser.
[MIKU] Class-change race, group
four, winner: Nozomi Kaminashi.
Hell yeah!
Hooray! She did it!
[NOZOMI]
Hey, nice fight, Fujisaki.
I had fun racin' ya.
I hope that we can
do it again sometime.
Whatever. Ugh. I told you.
I'm not interested in racing.
[MAN B] You've been
teasing me all this time
and now you won't do it.
[MAN A]
You know what you have to do
if you want me to
go any further.
[MAN B] I don't know
if I'm ready for that.
Huh? What the--?
I can't hear it.
I was so excited.
I've never felt that way
during a race before.
[KOTONE]
Nozomi Kaminashi, huh?
[NAGISA] First of all, I wanna
say good work, ladies.
Today's races were nail-biters.
It was almost too much
excitement for somebody my age.
I know this was a challenge,
but there's something important
I want you all to keep in mind.
And that's Setouchi Training
School's motto, "Only Land."
I wonder what that means.
[NAGISA] It's a reminder
that any fighting
between you and your
classmates is only on the Land.
The drama stays there.
Once the race is over, you're
united by an irreplaceable bond.
I know that some of you are
going to be disappointed
with today's results,
but remember,
you tried your best out there
and you should be
proud of yourselves.
Use any negativity you're
feeling to fuel your progress.
If you do that, then
you're bound to succeed
in the competitive
world of Keijo!
We'll be posting the class
promotion and demotion lists
this evening.
You ladies worked
really hard today,
so we're gonna be nice and
give you the day off tomorrow.
But everyone better
be ready to train hard
when we come back
the day after that.
You're dismissed.
[GIRLS]
Right!
[NAGISA] Kaminashi.
May I have a word with you?
[NOZOMI whimpers]
--[thud]
--[NOZOMI grunting]
[NOZOMI]
Please forgive me!
I'm sorry, Ms. Ujibe,
I know I was out of line
for using the Vacuum Butt Cannon
without your permission!
But I'm begging you,
don't spank me!
Dontcha think my rump's
been through enough?
[screams]
Uh?
[NAGISA]
Hmm...
[NAGISA] It looks like your
butt's gotten a bit thicker.
You're putting on muscle
in all the right places.
How do your hips feel?
Are you in any pain at all?
Yeah, but nowhere near
like it was before.
Interesting.
I never expected your
hips to get this strong
in a month's time.
If you ask me, this is proof
that you were born
to use the technique.
That said, it doesn't
change the fact
that using it could potentially
ruin your Keijo career.
You'll have to decide whether
it's worth the risk or not.
I'll allow you to start training
with the Vacuum Butt Cannon.
[NOZOMI gasps]
Thanks, Ms. Ujibe! I promise
I won't let you down, ma'am!
Your UTM really helped me!
[NAGISA]
Good to hear, but listen.
I need you to start taking
the sport of Keijo seriously.
You've gotta learn your
limitations and how to win
without putting unnecessary
stress on your body,
or you'll never make it to pro.
You shouldn't have used
it without asking me.
Uh. I'm sorry.
That probably would've
been a good idea,
but it's not like
I had a choice.
I would've lost without it.
No talking back!
[NOZOMI]
Yes, ma'am.
[NOZOMI] Aha! So this is
where you've been hidin'.
Hey. You okay?
Yeah, we were worried about ya.
[KAZANE] Kaminashi. This is
for you. I want you to have it.
'Kay, what is it?
[KAZANE]
It's the data I've gathered
on Setouchi's entire
student body.
[NOZOMI, NON, SAYAKA gasp]
[KAZANE] It's yours. I'm not
gonna need it anymore.
[NOZOMI]
Why's that, Kazane?
Well, you see,
I heard that every year
they kick some students out
after the class-change race.
And, um... I did so
poorly on mine today.
I'm sure they're
gonna let me go.
Come on, there's
somethin' you gotta see!
What is it?
[KAZANE gasps]
[NOZOMI] All four of us
made it into elite class!
But... how can that be?
I lost my race to Kusakai.
[NAGISA]
You're exactly right.
It'll go down in history
as an overwhelming
victory for Kusakai.
[NOZOMI]
Ms. Ujibe.
But I must say, I was impressed
by how well you performed
up until the very
end of the race.
You may not've even realized
you had her cornered, Aoba,
but I sure did.
In fact, you forced her to
use a forbidden technique.
"Forbidden"?
Which one did she use?
Titty Hypnosis.
It's a dangerous technique
to use on the pros,
much less amateur Keijo players.
That's why we forbid her
from ever using it at school.
[GIRLS]
Really?
But don't worry,
I've thoroughly punished
Kusakai for her actions.
Silly girl.
No!
[NOZOMI, NON chuckle]
I can't wait to see
how much you girls grow
in the next six months.
You never cease to amaze me.
[NOZOMI, NON, SAYAKA]
Thanks!
So does this mean
I get to stay here?
Yeah, you're stuck with us.
Like it or not.
Here's to another six months.
Let's do our best together.
[HITOMI] Don't you think you're
being a little too soft?
I mean, why promote
all four of them?
[NAGISA] I felt like
we had to take the chance.
Some people grow because
of their teammates.
Well, I trust you.
As I'm sure you have
a good reason for this.
Whatever it is.
[NAGISA]
You know it.
This'll be the year. We're
finally gonna defeat our rivals.
You know, the East.
[RIN]
It's falling!
[NOZOMI screams]
[NOZOMI]
Whoa, what's up with that girl?
[NOZOMI] Next Time:
"Alluring Kyoto Camp!"