[CROWD cheering]
[GUYS]
Yeah!
[CONTESTANT B chuckles]
[CROWD cheering]
[ANNOUNCER A] The battle between
boobs and butts continues!
With one move, Shirayuki,
the Missile Lady of Kyoto...
Aw, yeah! These
matches are so excitin'!
[NOZOMI]
Keijo.
This ladies-only
competition takes place
on a floating structure
called a Land.
The goal is to knock
your opponents off
using only your boobs and butt.
If you touch the Land with
anything other than your feet,
or if you get knocked
off, you lose.
[CONTESTANT B screams]
[CROWD gasps]
[NOZOMI gasps]
[NOZOMI]
In the end, the last competitor
who's left standing
on the Land...
...is the winner!
[ANNOUNCER A]
What a race!
Let's hear it for
today's champion, folks!
[NOZOMI] Not only do they
get bragging rights,
they get a huge cash prize!
[gasps]
[NOZOMI] I'm 18-year-old
Nozomi Kaminashi,
and when I graduate from
high school this spring,
I'm gonna be a Keijo player!
[GIRL A]
Oh, hey!
[GIRL B]
You made it!
[GIRL A]
Yeah.
[NOZOMI groaning]
Hold up! Miyata!
[sighs]
Why do you have so much?
You could've had it packed up
and sent here, you know.
But why waste the money
when I can do it for free?
Seems silly!
Why don't'cha help me out here?
Forget it, Nozomi.
You brought it,
you get to carry it.
C'mon! I'm giving you
the lightest one!
You can put it on top
of your rollie-bag!
Pretty please?
[NOZOMI squeals]
My journey to become a famous
Keijo player starts here!
[REPORTER A]
Are you excited to start
your first day of training?
You've made it into Setouchi!
Tell me, how's it feel?
[NOZOMI]
Wow! Look at all the reporters!
Who'd've thought girls
moving into a dorm
was worthy of news coverage?
That goes to show how
popular the sport is.
[NOZOMI]
Hello, gentlemen.
I'm Nozomi Kaminashi
from Shinminamoto
High School in Kobe.
Hyougo Prefecture!
I'm ready for my interview!
Who offers themselves
up to reporters?
Nozomi, get your stuff!
'Kay. Gimme a second!
Wait, is that Miyata?
[CAMERA MAN A]
No way! She's here?
Miss Sayaka Miyata.
What are your plans
now that you've made it
into Setouchi Keijo
Training School?
To do my best.
Can you tell us why you
choose this sport over Judo?
[REPORTER E]
More importantly,
what does your father
have to say about it?
Congrats on making
it to Setouchi.
I'm Shiomi with K-Sports.
May I take your photo?
Okay! Lemme straighten up.
[SATOMI] Just act natural. I
wanna get some candid shots.
I've noticed you and Miyata
have been attached at the hip
since you got here.
How do you know each other?
[NOZOMI]
Well, believe it or not,
we met at a hands-on
Keijo tryout.
And we've been friends
and rivals ever since.
I'm sure you know this,
but Miyata used to be a
famous Judo player before--
Just what do you
think you're doing?
Remember what I told you?
This year's elite class is full
of amazing Keijo players!
Don't waste your time
on some nobody, got it?
She may not be elite,
but she's a promising player!
Yeah right, it's pretty obvious
she made it in by sheer luck.
If you want a real interview,
talk to Rin Rokudou.
She ranked second on the exam.
Or hit up a thoroughbred
like Kotone Fujisaki.
With so many awesome
players to choose from,
why'd you pick the
girl most likely
to end up in "The Empty Room"?
'Cause she's the one to watch.
Those girls were great, but she
killed it at the entrance exam!
So tell me, what's your goal
now that you're here?
To be the richest Keijo
player in all of Japan!
Yay!
[HANABI]
Why, hello, Nozomi!
I haven't seen you in a while!
[NOZOMI]
Hey, what's up, Hanabi?
You passed!
That makes me so happy!
I was worried you'd fail and
I'd never get to see you again!
[NOZOMI chuckles]
Same here.
Wait a minute, why is your scarf
a different color than mine?
I dunno. Maybe 'cause
I'm in the elite class?
To be honest...
Hey, Sasaki, isn't that Kawai?
Yeah, she ranked
third on the exam.
Why is she talking
to that nobody?
[BOTH gasp]
[JUN]
Whoa, it's her.
[SATOMI] Her who?
She looks like a model.
[JUN]
Mio Kusakai.
She took first place
in the entrance exams.
You're Nozomi Kaminashi, right?
Yeah, but how'd ya know my name?
[MIO chuckles]
[MIO]
Hmm... Mm.
Your body's definitely well
balanced; perfect for Keijo!
Oh. Thank you, I guess.
[NOZOMI yelps]
Wow, totally my type!
You were right, Hanabi,
she's the cutest ever!
I told ya!
Sorry, I should
introduce myself.
I'm Mio Kusakai, 20 years
old. Love motorbikes.
But my favorite thing
in all the world
is havin' a little fun
with a cute girl.
I knew it! You've
got a great ass!
Careful, Mio, you're
gonna freak her out!
Better practice, 'cause
I'm lookin' forward
to competing against you.
I'll see ya!
[SAYAKA]
That was Mio Kusakai, wasn't it?
How'd you know?
She got the entrance
exam's top score.
[NOZOMI gasps]
[NOZOMI] If she's so awesome,
why'd she come talk to me?
You've certainly
become very popular.
I have to admit, I'm a
little envious, Nozomi.
[NOZOMI]
Of me?
[SAYAKA]
Where's your stuff?
[NOZOMI] Oh, crap!
I forgot! Lemme grab it.
Hey, wait up! Miyata!
[NOZOMI squeals]
[NOZOMI]
Back to where it all started!
Who cares about the dorms?
This is what I've
been dyin' to see!
[NOZOMI squeals]
Man, I can't wait to
get back on the Land!
So you can get
knocked off again?
That was a little
on the harsh side.
Way to make me feel
bad about myself.
But still, that loss just
got me more fired up
about playing Keijo.
These are the top ten players
in the rankings so far.
[NOZOMI] Why'd they
only list the top ten?
Didn't 40 girls move on?
They should just list
everyone who's passed.
It's for the players
who're trying to get
into the elite class.
Wait, the what now?
[SAYAKA] They told us about
it in orientation, remember?
There are some major perks
to being top ten elite.
They get a curriculum
that's more advanced
than the regular classes.
And they only have to pay
half of their tuition--
[NOZOMI]
What? They only pay half?
When you say "half," do you
mean they get like 50% off?
Well of course, what else
could it possibly mean?
Dummy.
Here we go, ladies.
It's time for the final test of
the Keijo athlete qualifiers.
We're gonna shake
things this round
with a mock race on a Road Land.
A Road Land? I've never
seen that type before.
The rules are the same
as a normal Keijo match:
You can't use your
hands or feet.
Fall off or touch the Land
with anything but your feet,
you fail.
Any questions before we begin?
Yes?
Since this is our last match,
will these results
determine our final grade?
[NAGISA] No, there are
other deciding factors
that we'll consider as well.
In the end, we'll take your
overall score into account.
[NOZOMI] Sure, but our
results on this test
will help determine our
overall score, right?
[NAGISA]
Yeah, of course.
So lemme get this straight,
if I knock more players
off than anybody else,
and I'm the last person left
standing on the Land...
...you're sayin' I still have
a shot at makin' it to the top!
[NAGISA]
Hm.
That's right.
[GIRLS cheering]
[NOZOMI]
I'm gonna do it! I'll show ya!
[NAGISA]
All right, everyone,
the final test for the Keijo
athlete qualifiers starts now!
Applicants'll be
put into groups of 12.
The allotted time for this
mock race is ten minutes.
Seems it'll be easier to
move around on this Land.
Whoa. I've never been on one
of these before, have you?
Yeah. It was the first time
I played against Miyata.
But that Land was a lot smaller
than this one and
not nearly as stable.
[SAYAKA]
It's certainly not as cramped,
so we've got plenty of
room to move around.
But I don't know if
that'll make it any easier.
It may actually require
more energy and focus
than the one at try-outs.
Five seconds until
the race begins.
Four. Three. Two. One.
[SAYAKA] Everyone's waiting to
see what their opponents do.
If we wanna attack,
we have to run across
this floating pathway.
[YUME]
What in the--?
I shouldn't've
let my guard down!
Whoa, what intense air pressure!
She's stronger than she looks!
Her butt muscles are incredible!
Hey, where're you goin'?
[SAYAKA]
Don't follow her, Nozomi.
[KAGAMI] You should really be
payin' attention, Princess.
Think you're tough?
You're not winnin' this round!
[SACHIKO] Your moves aren't too
shabby for a former Judo player.
[NOZOMI yelps]
[YUME] You underestimated
the difficulty of this Land.
Keep running like that,
you'll slip and fall.
This narrow path makes
it hard to balance.
As much as I hate it,
I guess I'll have to retreat.
No way! You snuck up on me!
I'm surrounded!
You're mine!
[gasps]
And she sticks the landing!
Looks like you're the
monkey in the middle!
[thud]
I'm not gonna let her win!
As soon as I knock
you off the Land,
I promise I'll finish her off.
[NOZOMI]
Take this! Butt Cannon!
[MIHO, YUME scream]
[MIKU] Number 565, Miki,
and number 489, Oono,
have fallen into the water!
Loser!
[chuckles]
Two down!
[KAGAMI, SAYO scream]
[MIKU]
Number 642, Oguri, and number...
I should've known.
Still using your speed
like you did in Judo.
I've found a method that works,
so why would I
bother to change it?
[ASUKA]
Sorry 'bout this,
but we gotta take you out
so we can survive.
[NOZOMI]
What do I do?
[HANABI] Move one step
to your left, please.
[chuckles]
Do you mind if I play, too?
[MIKU] Number 603, Nara, has
fallen into the water. Loser!
Whoa. Um. They're out cold.
[NOZOMI]
No way. What's with this girl?
She's knocking them out,
but how's she doing it?
[chuckles]
Aw, what's the matter?
You're afraid to take me on
without your friends to
back you up, aren't ya?
That's the thing with bullies,
they're really cowards.
Why, you!
[MIKU] Number 544, Iori,
has fallen. Loser!
Here she comes!
[NOZOMI gasps]
[NOZOMI]
She's fast!
A direct hit!
[HANABI gasps]
I'm glad I figured out
what happened to the others.
If I hadn't, I'd totally
be a goner right now.
Whaddaya mean?
I noticed you hit 'em
in the front of the jaw,
which shakes their brain
and knocks 'em out.
I had no clue Keijo players
used such awesome strategies.
Gotta say, I'm impressed!
If anyone's impressed, it's me,
'cause I thought I'd won!
I didn't expect you
to pull your jaw back
and slam your face into my butt!
To be honest, I was disappointed
by the lack of talent
in this mock battle.
But now I'm excited!
[SACHIKO]
Got you now!
You can't top me with
those mini melons!
[SACHIKO gasps]
[SACHIKO]
What the hell?
Those giant boobs were her butt?
[HANABI]
Sure-Kill.
Butt Guillotine!
Wow, you dodged it!
You just don't know
when to give up, do ya?
[NOZOMI]
This girl's insane!
It's like she's aiming
straight for my vital organs.
How'm I supposed to fight her
when I don't know which one
she's gonna shoot for next?
Only one thing to do!
Wha--?
It's my... Bust to Bust Attack!
[HANABI]
What're you doing?
[NOZOMI] Oh, please!
You know exactly what I'm doing.
As long as I'm this close,
you can't use your
pinpoint attacks!
[HANABI] Okay, you got me,
but the same goes for you!
It's not like you can attack
within close range!
Oh, yeah? Watch me!
[HANABI chuckles]
[HANABI] You want a real fight?
Fine, I won't hold back anymore.
Only one of us can
win and that's me.
No, I won't lose! I have to win!
Y'know, you're pretty
good at this.
You've got plenty of power but
you need to learn how to use it.
I'll teach you.
Lesson one: Boobs can
do more than push.
I may be new to Keijo,
but I'm not stupid.
I know what they can do!
[HANABI laughs]
Oh, goodie! That was
fun! You're amazing!
[MIKU]
Thirty seconds remaining!
[NOZOMI] I won't get anywhere
if I just keep pushing into her.
This time I'll go in hard
and knock her off!
Thought you could attack me?
You already tried
that move on me.
Looks like you're
running out of tricks!
You're goin' down!
I don't get it.
No one's ever broken down
my moves this fast before!
I've had it with you!
[NOZOMI]
This is it! Game over!
[NAGISA]
Kawai dodged her attack!
Nozomi!
[NAGISA] And used the opening
to hit Kaminashi's jaw!
[HANABI]
Down you go!
This match was fun!
Thanks for playin'.
Let's do it again sometime.
[NOZOMI]
I can't believe it. I lost.
There are so many
strong competitors.
Keijo is... amazing!
[NOZOMI]
Everything changed that day.
I always thought
I'd be satisfied
just bein' another Keijo
player, you know?
The salary is great,
the competitions are fun,
and you get to travel
all across the country.
But then, I tried my best to win
a race and I ended up losing.
That experience changed
my whole way of thinking.
I wanna win more than anything.
I was sure I flunked out.
So imagine my surprise when I
got my letter sayin' I passed.
But I'm still so
angry with myself
for bein' a pathetic loser.
We'll both get stronger
if we work hard.
It just takes time.
I've been meanin' to ask,
why'd you start playin' Keijo?
From what I've heard you were
pretty awesome at Judo.
I guess so.
This might sound weird, but I
like wearing cute swimsuits.
Uh. You know what I mean!
If you're a popular player,
then you get a personal
swimsuit designer.
It's their job to create a
signature suit just for you.
I've always thought that
would be kinda cool.
I dunno. I've got other reasons
but it doesn't matter.
[CROWD cheering]
[NOZOMI] Oh! I can't wait
to get out there again!
[SAYAKA]
Me either.
You'll find your room
numbers listed on the wall.
Well? Have you found
your name yet?
No. It's not up there.
If neither of us are listed,
it can only mean one thing.
Looks like you're gonna be
stuck with me as a roomie.
Hooray.
[YUKO]
Like it or not,
you guys are definitely
sharing a room.
Hey, Ooshima! This
means you passed, huh?
Of course I did!
There's one problem.
[YUKO groans]
I did so poorly on
the exam's mock race
that they bumped me down from
elite class to regular class.
That said, I think you
guys might actually
have it worse than me.
[NOZOMI]
Whaddaya mean?
I hate to tell ya, but the room
you're in, 309, is kinda cursed.
From what I've been told, it's
known as the "Empty Room."
Why do they call it that?
[YUKO] Apparently it's where
they send the students
most likely to quit Setouchi
because they can't keep
up with the classes.
They call it the "Empty Room"
because it empties out
so fast every semester.
[NOZOMI]
What? Are you serious?
This is where they send
the failures, huh?
How did we end up
in this stupid room?
I mean, we're winners!
[SAYAKA]
Let's just go in.
[NON chuckles]
We'll be joining the
Empty--Uh! Room 309!
Hey, we're your roommates.
I'm Nozomi Kaminashi.
I'm so thrilled to be
in here, I could scream!
My name is Sayaka Miyata.
Nice to meet you.
Hi! It's a pleasure
to meet you both.
Anyway, I'm Non Toyoguchi.
I look forward to getting
to know you ladies better.
Wow! Your voice is
too stinkin' cute!
[NON] Uh! I almost forgot,
I brought something for you.
It's a little treat
from my hometown.
[NOZOMI]
How thoughtful of you!
[SAYAKA] Um. Thank you.
May I ask where you're from?
[NON] Believe it or not,
I came all the way...
[NOZOMI]
Um. Hey, there.
Oh, hi. I'm Kazane Aoba.
'Kay. Is that all you got?
So do you have a preference
for which bed you get?
I would imagine the closer
you are to the hallway,
the louder that it'll...
...be!
Oh, no!
Uh-oh! Are you okay?
Why wouldn't I be?
[NOZOMI] That looked like
it hurt. You're even crying!
[yelps]
[NON]
No, I'm not!
You're seeing things.
I'm perfectly fine!
[NOZOMI] You're not foolin' me.
Your nose is bright red.
Don't know what
you're talking 'bout!
My friends and family back home
are always saying
how clumsy I am.
[NOZOMI, SAYAKA]
Can ya really blame 'em?
They tried to talk me out
of being a Keijo player,
but I didn't listen.
I'm gonna to go out there and
make a name for mah village!
Your what?
Mah village back home
in Kagoshima, silly!
People'a been movin' away
but I got a plan! Ha!
Ah reckon gettin' famous'll
bring tourists to town.
[NOZOMI, SAYAKA]
You "reckon"?
Ah! Ah'm doin' it again!
What in tarnation's
gotten into me?
I try to hide my accent so
I'm easier to understand.
Yeah, you're gonna
have to try harder.
Anyway, let's work together
to make our training awesome!
Whaddaya say? You in, Aoba?
[NOZOMI, SAYAKA]
Whoa. No reaction at all!
[sighs]
Great, my roommates have
such unique personalities.
I'm not looking forward to this.
[NOZOMI]
Hey, what's that you're readin'?
Cool! A Keijo mag! Would you
mind if I take a look?
Aw, c'mon, just a quick peek!
[SAYAKA] I should've known
she'd turn out to be
the biggest troublemaker
of them all!
I'm so sorry! Help me out here!
Uh, Toyoguchi? Happen
to have any tape on ya?
Yeah. But all I've
got is duct tape.
Great! That should do the trick!
Don't even try it, Stupid!
Hey, guys. Please calm down.
I can't take-- Ah!
Not again!
[NON yelping]
Safe!
You're not safe, you ditz!
You spilled tea on my bed!
[NON screams]
[NON]
Oh mah goodness gracious!
Ah'll have it wiped
up in a jiffy!
[NOZOMI]
Here, use this rag, Toyoguchi!
[KAZANE] No! Don't wipe my bed
down with that nasty thing!
[NON]
Ah'm sorry!
[NOZOMI]
Wow, Non,
your accent's the funniest
thing I've ever heard!
[SAYAKA]
I'm going to die in this room.
[NAGISA]
Okay, up next is room 309.
Don't you worry, ladies.
I promise I'll go easy on ya.
Siren? More like seal!
[NOZOMI] Next time, "The Hip
Toss Brings Us Together!"