Namu.
[chuckles]
Wow, seems like
the infighter team
had a pretty rough day.
They sure look exhausted.
They must've raced
with their instructor, too.
I guess their's is hardcore.
Well, I'm gonna head
to the showers.
'Kay, see ya later.
Oh, hey. Is something wrong?
The rest of the infighters
are hanging out in the lobby.
Listen, Miyata.
Ya think, maybe you could
help me out with somethin'?
[SAYAKA] You need help?
From me? Sure, what's up?
[gasps]
U-Um! Why're you
taking off your clothes?
Well, whaddaya think?
What do you think of my body?
I, uh--
[NOZOMI]
Are my boobs proportionate?
I can't really tell.
My nips are kind of
a weird shape, huh?
Are they the right color,
or are they too dark?
[SAYAKA]
Uh. I dunno what to say.
[NOZOMI]
Okay, well then in that case...
What about my backside?
[NOZOMI] Do ya notice anything
strange about my butt?
Like, is my crack off-center?
C'mon, you can tell me, Miyata.
I would do the same for you!
[SAYAKA]
You're being a total creep!
[NOZOMI]
No, wait!
Shirayuki told you
that your body has a flaw.
Now you're freaked
and trying to figure out
what could be wrong with you.
Why didn't you just
tell me that before?
Instead you stripped down
and came at me all naked.
I didn't know what to do!
Sorry.
You know, it's funny
'cause that's so you.
There's such
a giant gap of power
between me and my instructor.
I'm not even thinkin'
about tryin' to
beat 'em in a race or anything.
Trust me, I'm not tryin'
to defeat Shirayuki--
that ain't happenin'.
The thing is,
I couldn't do anything at all
and that's what scares me.
Why's it scare you?
We got a lotta work
to do in six months.
When we go pro,
there's no room for excuses--
skill is all that matters.
It's one thing
if I go out and lose
'cause I'm not good enough,
but I don't wanna go out there
thinkin' that
I'll lose every match.
The more I thought about
what Shirayuki said,
the more it put me at a loss.
I dunno where to go
from here, y'know?
Well then,
maybe you should watch
Shirayuki's moves more closely.
Whaddaya mean?
See, I would pay attention
to her every move
and compare it to my own.
It may be the only way
to figure out
the flaw she mentioned to you.
[NAGISA] Excellent work today.
Thank you, Shirayuki.
No problem. I want them to win
as much as you do.
Once we feel like they've
got the basics down,
we're going to make them
wear UTMs while training.
Everybody will wear it?
It might sound crazy
but we think these girls
can change the sport of Keijo.
[SHIRAYUKI] After this
training camp you've got
the East-West War, right?
Yes. So tell me,
what do you think of them?
You've brought some
amazing athletes to this camp.
Aren't they wonderful?
And that Kaminashi girl--
she's fascinating.
I agree. Do think you could
look after her a bit more?
Yeah, I'd love to.
Okay ladies, first
we'll get in the water,
and then we're gonna start
walking up the river.
[HANABI, ATSUKO, MIO]
Yes, ma'am.
I really dunno if I can
figure out my weak point
just by watchin' her, but
I guess it can't hurt to try.
Hmmm...
[NOZOMI] Her posture's awesome.
She keeps her back straight.
Her swimsuit is
super cute. What else?
Let's make like
a bread truck and haul buns!
[NOZOMI]
And she likes lame jokes.
Oh, wow,
this water feels amazing!
The current's stronger
than I thought it'd be.
This is tough, so I can see how
it'll help train
our lower bodies.
[ATSUKO]
This is my kinda training!
My Ass of Vajra
is gonna get even stronger!
[NOZOMI screams]
What happened? Are you okay?
A twig got caught
in my cleavage and it scared
the ever-lovin' crap outta me.
Man, Shirayuki's really fast.
I can't believe she's
already so far ahead.
[HANABI] What do you expect
from an active pro?
I can't get over
how strong she is--
she's like, super-human.
She kicked my butt
in our introduction race,
like, seriously whooped me.
And now I'm struggling
to even keep up with her.
This is so depressing.
[chuckles]
Yeah, right?
[NOZOMI] She's moving through
the water so elegantly.
It's like she's not even
fightin' the current
when she walks.
But it's not just
her hips and legs
that're helpin' her get through.
She's also usin'
her breasts to knock
any debris outta the way.
[SHIRAYUKI grunts]
Haaauh!
[NOZOMI] It's hard to believe
she can swing her boobs around
like that in
a current this strong.
Wait a sec--she's not just
trainin' her upper body,
she's working on
her lower half, too!
It looks like we're
doin' the same trainin'
as she is, but we're not.
We're only doin' half the work.
[groans]
Take this.
I can do it.
Should I go right or left?
Nngh! Owie!
[HANABI]
Oh no, not again.
Ouch, that looked like it hurt.
I get it now.
She's also workin' on
her decision-makin' skills.
[NOZOMI]
For this one...
[grunts]
I did it. I thought
it'd be harder
to knock that big one away.
Whoa. I think I might've
figured it out.
A weaker attack
that's hard to read.
Or a powerful attack
that's easy to read.
Yeah, that's it!
My butt's too big!
[NOZOMI grunting]
So tell me, how'd I do?!
[SAYAKA] Well, you're much
slower than before.
What's slowing her down?
I'm not sure
but her figure eights
are going wider now.
I'll explain.
She gained a lot of muscle
in her tush when
she was training for
the Vacuum Butt Cannon.
And normally, that would
be a good thing,
but the added weight is
making it harder to control.
[KAZANE humming]
[NON]
Mmmm!
[shrieking]
Kinda like that?
Yeah, I guess so.
Look on the bright side.
That means you can hit
with ton of power!
As long as you can do that,
you're golden, right?
[NOZOMI]
Mmmm...?
[SHIRAYUKI]
No, that's not enough.
[NOZOMI] Shirayuki.
What're you doin' here?
[SHIRAYUKI]
Late night training.
Look, it doesn't matter
how strong your attack may be,
if the build-up's that obvious
then it'll never work
in the pros.
[gasps]
Kaminashi. Listen closely.
If you want to use
the Vacuum Butt Cannon,
you're gonna have to
take your butt to the limit.
Of course I wanna use it.
It's just... I don't even
know where to begin!
--[beeping]
--[SHIRAYUKI gasps]
Oh no, look at the time.
I'm going to miss "See the
World" by Bay Window.
We'll continue
this chat tomorrow.
Take it to the limit?
[indistinctive chattering]
Sheesh, it looks tight.
It's definitely gonna
take some getting used to.
This swimsuit is so snug
that it's hard to move around.
I don't wanna sound
weird or anything,
but it sure does makes your
ta-tas look bigger, Kazane.
You would think it'd have
the opposite effect, you know?
[KAZANE] You're right,
they do look bigger.
Ugh, how embarrassing.
Don't be embarrassed,
you look great!
I bet I look pretty good
in this thing, too!
[RIN]
Mhmm!
You've got a perfect
hour glass shape.
I'd guess you're prob'ly
a G or an H-cup!
Why thank you, Rin.
You're lookin' quite
boobalicious yourself!
[SAYAKA] If I wear this, it'll
make my breasts look bigger?!
Goodness, this thing's
even tighter than I thought.
Like my bosoms, boys?
They're so bouncy!
[RIN]
No they are not.
Wait, it's not what
you're thinking--I was just--!
We should probably
apologize, huh?
Why? You don't have to do that!
We're sorry, Miyata.
Wait, this is about my
lack of bounciness, isn't it?
[SHIRAYUKI] You need to
be able to stand up straight.
These gals can move
around right after
puttin' the damn thing on?
It took me an entire month
of blood, sweat, and tears.
Hey, Kawai.
Your balance is weak,
you're wiggling
around everywhere.
I know it's hard,
but you need to practice
maintaining your posture.
Hold for thirty seconds.
I don't know if I can
hold it that long, ma'am!
[SHIRAYUKI] Give it a try.
Yoshida and Kusakai,
you can go ahead and move on
to the next exercise.
--Sure.
--Yes, ma'am.
You and I are going to a
different location, Kaminashi.
Uh. Right!
[FARMER'S WIFE 7A]
Oh yes, my husband told me
about what's going on.
[SHIRAYUKI]
Thank you for helping us.
If you want to take
your butt to the limit,
like I mentioned
to you last night,
then you're going to
have to learn
a new way to attack with it.
So you're gonna
teach me a new technique?
[SHIRAYUKI] That's correct.
You need a compact move
with a sharp edge
and I know just the one.
In the Keijo lexicon
it's called the Butt Flash.
The Butt Flash?
[SHIRAYUKI]
Okay, young lady.
I want to you to get
to work pulling turnips.
You have got to be
kiddin' me here.
This is my trainin'?
You're not going to be
doing it the normal way.
[grunts]
You'll use your butt
to pull them from the earth.
[NOZOMI] What? I can definitely
say this is something
I've never tried before.
But what does this
have to do with
the Butt Flash technique
she's supposed to teach me?
[NOZOMI grunts]
All I got was the leaves!
Right, that's because you're
not using your power properly.
I don't understand
what I'm doin' wrong.
Okay, that's the last time
I'm tying it for you.
Now give me a quick,
precise attack!
Uh... right!
--[grunts]
--[crunch]
--[SHIRAYUKI] Faster!
--[NOZOMI] Yes, ma'am!
[SHIRAYUKI] There's one thing
I forgot to mention.
The deal I made
with the farmer said
we have to purchase
every turnip we ruin.
But, that's gonna be
a lot of 'em.
Better figure it out fast
or you and your classmates
will be eating
nothing but turnips
for the foreseeable future.
Seriously? Okay fine,
but I really don't see
how this exercise
is gonna help me
sharpen my butt attacks.
I promise it'll all makes sense
when you pull out a turnip.
Well, good luck to you,
young lady!
Wha--?
--[NOZOMI grunting]
--[crunching]
[panting]
You've made quite a mess.
I hope your friends
like turnips.
[NOZOMI] There's gotta be
a trick to this, right?
Why dontcha
just show me? Please?
Sorry, I can't do that.
Your body needs
to learn the motion
and that's going
to take repetition.
[whines]
[NOZOMI]
I'm gonna give my all this time!
[grunts]
[NOZOMI]
Uh!
Now that I think about it,
this is prob'ly
hard for her too.
She's an athlete, not a teacher.
There's a good chance
that she's never
had to teach anyone before.
For all I know she could be
makin' up this Butt Flash thing.
[FARMER 7A]
Hello, Kyouko!
[SHIRAYUKI]
Hi there!
I didn't know
you were back in town.
I wish you would've told me!
Sorry 'bout that. I should've
let everyone know.
No, it's not a big deal.
I'm just happy
that I got to see ya.
Wait, are you out here
trainin' that young lady?
That's awfully nice
of you considering
you're so busy
with your own races.
[FARMER 7A]
Well, keep up the good work.
When you get into S-Class
we're gonna have a big party.
Thank you.
I'll do my best, sir!
I know that Kyoto's
part of your schtick
but you actually grew up here.
--Yeah.
--What did he mean?
About you being busy, ma'am?
Everyone in town
knows I'm trying to
secure a promotion this fall.
So I need to win
every race I have scheduled
between now and then.
Not just for the promotion,
but for the people
who are cheering me on.
[NOZOMI]
What is wrong with me?
How could I be so self-absorbed?
I didn't even consider
that I might be
takin' up Shirayuki's
precious time.
I was too busy questioning
her training methods.
--Get back to it.
--Yes, ma'am!
[NOZOMI]
I've gotta trust her!
I'm gonna do my best to master
the Butt Flash technique!
[NOZOMI grunting]
[grunts]
[NOZOMI grunts]
[sighs]
This is much better.
[NON] Those UTMs are
so tight they're worse than
a sports bra, y'know?
Feels good to take it off.
Yeah.
[SAYAKA grunts]
[ALL gasp]
[NOZOMI]
I need to move my butt faster!
Take that! And that!
[SAYAKA]
Hey! Let us relax in peace!
[sighs]
I could stay here all day.
Man, this sucks.
My muscles's are stiff
after wearin' that suit.
[NON]
Don't worry, it'll get easier.
So I heard the outfighters have
been practicing team play.
That must be a lot fun!
[RIN] Yeah, but it's harder
than you'd think.
You can't just fight, you've
gotta look out for your allies.
You know, Rin-rin.
I'll bet Aoba's
great at team play.
[KAZANE]
No, not really.
I'd be cool with any
teammate but Toyoguchi.
[NON]
Mmmmmm?!
Sorry, hon,
but you have to admit
you've got a case
of the clumsies.
Ain't that the truth.
We almost died the other day!
Hey, quit bein' so mean!
I might be a little clumsy
sometimes, but what's it matter?
I'm still an elite,
just like you!
I'm perfectly capable
of holding my own!
[SAYAKA] Here's the thing. I
wanna believe you, I really do.
[NON]
Thanks, Sayaka!
[SAYAKA] But you keep giving me
reasons to doubt you.
Like right now, for instance.
Do you realize you're wearing
my bra and panties?
[NON] Uhh... Goodness gracious,
I got into the wrong locker!
Please forgive me!
I was wonderin' why
my bra was so tight
all of a sudden.
What?
[KAZANE] Calm down, Miyata!
She didn't mean to be rude!
[MIKU] Ladies. Would you
please meet me in the lobby
as soon as you're
finished changing?
Time flies. And now
we have less than a month
to prepare for
the East-West War.
The what now?
How do you not know
about the East-West War?
I doubt that she bothered
to read the curriculum.
Eeeh!
[RIN]
As popular as Keijo is,
there are only
two schools in the country.
Setouchi Keijo
Training School in the west,
and Suruga Keijo
Training School in the east.
Once a year there's an event
where the best players
from each school compete.
It's called the East-West War.
I've never heard of
it before, but I am so in!
[KAZANE] It's the whole reason
we came to this training camp.
It's to prepare us
for the East-West War.
This is your opportunity
to show your friends and family
how far you've come.
So take these
and be sure to invite
your loved ones.
Think of it as a way of
thanking them for their support.
Guess I prob'ly should've
read the curriculum.
I hope my family can make it.
Think yours will, Miyata?
You said that you talked to 'em
when you got here, right?
Did ya get to talk to your dad?
No. I didn't. 'Cause he
refused to get on the phone.
I can't blame him. I mean,
he owns a judo dojo,
and his own daughter
rejected the sport
and ran off to play Keijo.
[NOZOMI]
He'll get over it.
You might as well
invite them, right?
I betcha they'll come to watch.
They'll understand once
they get to see you compete.
You better wear
your cutest swimsuit.
[indistinctive chatter]
Oh, wow. Nothing but
turnips, huh?
[NOZOMI chuckles nervously]
[NOZOMI] If I focus my energy
and yank my butt quickly,
I should be able to get it out!
Ugh! What the heck's
wrong with me?!
I don't get it! I'm pullin'
'em as hard as I can,
but no matter how quick I move,
it's still not fast enough
to pull 'em out whole!
I keep trying over
and over again,
but it's just not happenin'!
I can't believe
how bad I suck at this.
I'm really startin'
to hate turnips.
[MIO]
Hiya, cutie!
You know, I never pictured
you as the farming type.
What's up, Kusakai?
Ms. Shirayuki sent me here
to take you back to the group.
Why? Is it lunch time already?
She's got you doing
some weird training.
Are you pulling turnips
with your butt?
Can you believe it?
It's a lot harder
than you would think.
This is my second day at it,
and I've yet to pull a single--
Hang on, missy, just what
do you think you're doin'?
I'm telling ya, it looks easy
but it's actually very--
--[MIO grunts]
--[NOZOMI gasps]
Yaaaay!
[laughing]
That was fun! No wonder
you've been hiding here!
[NOZOMI] No way. She totally
pulled one out on her first try.
Just kill me now.
I've been at it
for two days with no luck
and then you come along
and do it no problem.
I feel like I'm wastin'
my time tryin' so hard.
Sorry. I can't help
that I'm a genius.
[NOZOMI grunts]
Lemme get this straight,
your butt gained muscle
from training and now you're
having trouble controlling it
'cause it's heavier, right?
Yeah, so?
Maybe you should try using
the muscles you've gained--
y'know, the ones
that caused this problem?
Huh, I haven't tried that yet.
So you're saying I can
use my butt muscles
to pull the turnips out whole.
That's the only hint you get.
You're gonna have to figure
the rest out on your own.
Aw. C'mon Kusakai,
don't leave me hangin'.
I could use all
of the help I can get!
Okay. How 'bout
you come to my bed tonight
and I'll teach you
everything I know.
[shrieks]
Listen, just forget
that I said anything!
I'll figure it out on my own.
Aw. Don't be shy.
Come on, it'll be fun.
[NOZOMI] No means no!
Now get your hands off me!
What the hell is wrong with you?
Nozomi Kaminashi!
I know turnips are good for us
and all, but this is crazy.
What I wouldn't give
for some plain ol'
eggs and rice right now.
[NOZOMI]
This is all my fault.
--[NOZOMI grunting]
--[crunching]
I've been givin' it
my best shot but
I still haven't
pulled one out.
Ugh! Why does this have
to be so friggin' hard?
Kusakai was able
to do it on her first try.
I'm thinkin'
these stupid turnips
have somethin'
against me! Aaaah!
Wait a second.
When I knocked the
cart back earlier,
it pulled me back with it.
But why'd that happen?
[NOZOMI]
That's it!
If I think of the turnips
as the muscles in my butt,
then there's no downside
to havin' extra weight.
[thunder rumbles]
[BOTH]
Uh?
[FARMER 7A] Aah!
I need to picture it in my head.
If I imagine
my butt as a weight,
then all I've gotta do is
loosen it up as I raise it,
then yank it quickly.
And that should create
enough momentum!
I can't help
but wonder if the exercise
was a little too hard for her.
Maybe I should just
tell her how it's done. Mm?
Girl, you're lucky
I like turnips.
[laughs]
I know you're eating,
ladies, but listen up.
As you know, tomorrow's the last
day of our elite training camp.
We've decided to conduct
mock races so that
we can see how much
you've improved.
Normally, we would pick
your opponents but we thought
we'd give you the opportunity
this time around.
So if there's anyone
you'd like to fight,
please just let me know.
We can pick our opponents?
It's nice they're letting us
choose but all I know
is who I don't wanna fight.
Ah! I know who I want to go up--
[USAGI] Right here.
I'm Usagi Tsukishita
and I wanna challenge
Nozomi Kaminashi to a race.
[NOZOMI]
Mm?
[gulps]
[GIRL gasps]
Don't underestimate us.
Setouchi'll thrash you!
[NOZOMI] Next time:
"The Dramatic East-West War!!!!"