Man, it's just the usual
rice with raw egg on top,
but it tastes different somehow.
Huh, I wonder what's
changed all of a sudden.
[NON] They must use
fancier ingredients
to make the elite class's meals!
[NOZOMI]
Mh-hm!
Why're you acting like
this is news to you?
We've had this conversation
before, Nozomi.
I know! I'm just so happy
to be in elite class!
[NARRATOR] In the past,
gamblers have been limited
to horse, bike, boat,
and car races.
But now there's a new form
of legalized gambling
sweeping the nation.
It's called Keijo!
Players compete to be
the last girl standing
atop a floating platform
called a "Land."
The kicker? They can only
use their boobs and butts!
The question is:
Who will rule the Land?
Will it be the 18-year-old
Nozomi Kaminashi?
She's one of the
many young ladies
whose search for fame
and fortune has lead them
to the world of Keijo!
And this is the story of their
journey to becoming champions!
[NOZOMI] Honshu's really grown
since the last time I visited.
I mean, this is one heck
of a bridge, huh?
[NON]
Yeah, it's gigantic!
I don't think I've ever
seen one this big before.
[NOZOMI] Right after we were
promoted to the elite class,
we were told that we
would be heading to Kyoto
for a special Keijo
training camp.
Apparently it's a yearly event
where a select group of students
partake in a bunch of trainin'.
I don't get why we
can't do it in Awaji,
but whatever, I'll go
along for the ride.
[NOZOMI] So where are
all of the instructors?
You'd think that they
woulda been here by now.
Do ya think maybe we took
a wrong turn or something?
Ladies, let's not resort
to idle chatter.
Remember why we're here,
former residents of room 309.
You must stay focused and
ready to learn at all times.
I just contacted the inn
where we'll be staying.
Unfortunately, they don't
have our rooms ready yet
so we can't check in
for a few hours.
Really?
I honestly didn't think we'd
make it here this early.
There's usually a lot more
traffic on the freeway.
Because of our predicament,
we've decided to give you
three hours of free time
to explore Kyoto.
We get to venture
out on our own?
For real, you're seriously
gonna let us go check out Kyoto?
That's correct.
Aw, yeah! I'm so glad our
chaperone is Ms. Kobayakawa!
She's a friggin' goddess!
Well, given the hellish
regime you're gonna be on,
you should have some fun
while you can, right?
[GIRLS] Wait, what're
they gonna make us do?
Now I'm kinda scared.
[NOZOMI]
Anyone got a plan?
I would've looked
up things to do,
but I didn't bother 'cause
I figured we'd be trainin'
the whole time we're here.
Yeah, I know, right?
I don't even know
where to start.
Well, uh...
I know! Why don't
we have a party
to get to know one another?
[NOZOMI]
I dunno.
Why not? You guys
are the newbie elites.
Surely you wanna
meet your classmates.
Now's as good a time
as ever, dontcha think?
[NOZOMI]
I guess so.
I grew up in Kyoto
so I'd be happy
to show you ladies around
town if you'd like.
[NON, NOZOMI]
Mh-hm!
Awesome!
There's this cute little café
a few blocks from here
where a bunch of
super-hot guys hang out.
Super-hot guys?
Yeah! Whaddaya say,
you wanna go?
Who knows, maybe one of us'll
meet the man of our dreams!
Can you imagine?
We'll sneak out at night to meet
our new lover by the Kamo River.
[SAYAKA, NON, NOZOMI]
What happened to getting to
know each other?
I dunno. I just don't think
that's such a good idea.
Oh, come on! We're
talkin' about hot guys!
Uh. Yeah.
I get it, but that wouldn't
be fair to poor Kazane
'cause she's terribly shy.
Please! I can't talk
to men I don't know!
[NON]
I'm sorry, Kazane.
[HANABI] This is your
shot at romance, girl!
[SAYAKA clears throat]
Hey, I know. Why don't
you go see Kyoto with me?
How 'bout a friendly
game of truth or dare?
[NOZOMI]
I don't think so!
Um. What's the deal
with "truth or dare"?
I've never played it.
What? It's only the
coolest game in history!
I could dare you lovely
ladies to share pocky with me!
I'd get to hear your
deepest secrets...
[NOZOMI, NON, KAZANA]
Kusakai, you're hot as hell,
but sometimes you're
down right creepy.
So I'm gonna have to pass.
Aw! Please play with me!
Then how 'bout you guys
come sight seeing with--
Whatcha doin' with your
free time, Kaminashi?
I'm gonna go work out
if you wanna join.
I heard there's an
awesome gym nearby.
[KOTONE] If you're bored, I can
lend you one of my drama CDs.
Uh. Thanks! Next time.
[SAYAKA]
Dummy.
[sighs]
What has gotten into me?
This is silly. Why'd
I come here by myself?
This is no different
than when I was a kid.
[GIRL A]
Hey, Sayaka.
A big group of kids are gonna go
and watch the fireworks
after school tomorrow.
Do you wanna come along with us?
[SAYAKA] Tomorrow?
Um, once practice is over--
Dummy!
You're being so inconsiderate.
Don't bother Sayaka.
She can't watch
fireworks with us
'cause she's got Judo practice.
No, wait. I've got some
time off tomorrow--
[GIRL B] She goes straight
to her family's dojo
after school every day.
Isn't that right, Sayaka?
Oh. I'm sorry. I hope
I didn't upset you.
Uh-uh. I'm not upset.
I wish she could hang
out, but she can't.
--[GIRL D] I wanna snow cone!
--[GIRL E] What should we do?
[BOY B] The fireworks
are gonna be awesome!
Now here I am, stuck
touring Kyoto by myself.
[NOZOMI] Hey, what's up,
lil' lady? You a local?
You're a cutie.
So did I fool ya?
What're you doing here?
I thought you went
with the others.
Nope, they're nice and all,
but I decided I just
wanna hang out with you.
I hope that's okay.
Now what? Any ideas where
we should head next?
Huh?
What's the matter, Miyata?
Wow, you play dirty.
You always seem like you're so
oblivious, but it's all an act.
Look! There they are!
We found you! We've been
searching all over for you guys!
[SAYAKA] Seriously? Guess
all my friends play dirty.
Hey, Miyata!
[NON screams]
Ouch! You took a major
tumble! Are you okay, Non?
[NON]
Whaddaya mean? I didn't fall!
I meant to do that, I swear!
I was pretendin' to slide
into base 'cause I'm happy!
[SAYAKA] Sorry, but
nobody's gonna buy that.
Nice try though!
[NON] Anyway, I found a place
that looks like a lot of fun.
You guys wanna check it out?
We can always move
on if it's lame.
[MIKU] I know I said that you
could do whatever you wanted
with your free time,
but come on,
don't you think you might've
gone a tad overboard?
Just look at all that stuff!
Yeah, maybe.
[MIKU] I'll be confiscating all
of that, thank you very much.
I'll be holding on to your
personal belongings
while you're busy
with training camp.
[NOZOMI]
At least let me eat...
[MIKU] Young lady,
hand it over right now.
Give it to me!
I'll eat it later and
tell you how tasty it was.
[NOZOMI] Aw man, that was
the only souvenir I got.
Listen up, everyone.
Before we arrive,
allow me to explain
what we'll be doing at this
special training camp.
You'll be divided into groups
based on your player type:
Infighter, outfighter,
or counter.
Each group will then be given
a dedicated instructor
who will lead you
through your training.
Basically, they're the boss.
Excuse me. I haven't been
assigned a player type.
Oh, I forgot!
Ms. Ujibe has a message for you.
For now, she wants you
to train as an infighter.
At least while you're
at this training camp.
So that'll be your group.
I'm an infighter.
[laughs]
[NOZOMI] Now I can
start trainin' in a way
that matches my strengths!
That means you'll be with me!
We're gonna have
some fun, Nozomi!
Yeah! This is gonna be amazin'!
She's so fired up.
[NOZOMI] Ah. So this is
where we'll be stayin', huh?
It looks pretty nice.
You're right.
I was imaginin' somethin'
a little more run-down.
But this place isn't so bad.
[NOZOMI] I'm tellin' you,
rickshaws are super-fast!
I would know 'cause
I rode on one today!
Huh, whaddaya mean what
am I doin' in Kyoto? Ha!
I'm at a special training
camp along with...
Somethin' about not
havin' a cell phone
makes me wanna talk to
my family a lot more.
I know, right?
It's like all I want
is to hear their voices.
[NOZOMI] ...become a
B-class Keijo player...
[RIN] Kaminashi sure
is taking her time.
[HANABI]
No kidding.
[NOZOMI]
...and win big prize money!
Basically, everything's
goin' great!
[SAYAKA]
Hello, Mom?
I'm fine. Thanks for asking.
Is Dad home?
[SAYAKA'S MOM]
Honey! Phone call from Sayaka!
[sighs]
[SAYAKA'S MOM]
Listen, dear. I'm sorry.
No. It's no big deal.
But thanks for trying, Mom.
I'll talk to you later.
[SAYAKA'S MOM]
Hang in there, Sayaka.
[MIKU] For this training camp,
you're going to be rooming
with members of your
player type group.
It makes things easier
when your roommates
are on the same schedule
and allows you to stay
with your instructors.
What a bummer! Sorry,
Miyata, Kazane, and Non.
I'm gonna miss you guys.
[HANABI] C'mon, let's go
check out our room, Nozomi!
We'll miss you too!
I kinda feel sorry for her.
[NOZOMI]
Oh! This room's enormous!
[ATSUKO] If I catch ya in
here again, I'll report ya.
[whines]
[USAGI]
I just wanna see my beloved!
Hey, who was that weirdo?
Uh? You've never met her before?
Guess you could say she worships
Kusakai. She's a groupie.
[chuckles]
[HANABI]
Her name's Usagi Tsukishita
and she's an outfighter
in the elite class.
[HANABI]
She doesn't really stick out,
but I think she's
a cutie, don't you?
Looks like this is my chance.
[chuckles]
Yep, she's tiny and cute
just like a lil' bunny rabbit.
Would you quit fondling
me while you're talking?
[MIO] I can't help it,
they're a perfect handful!
[NOZOMI] You're seriously
creepin' me out!
[HANABI] I wanna fondle them,
too! Can I? Pretty please?
[USAGI] I'll get you for this,
Nozomi Kaminashi!
How dare you steal my beloved
Kusakai's affections from me!
[NOZOMI whines]
What're those? Weights?
Yeah.
I figured I might as well train
my legs while we're out runnin'.
You did that on your own? Wow!
You're way into your training
lately, aren't ya, Kaminashi?
Woohoo! We are seriously
rockin' our run today!
[NOZOMI laughs]
[RIN]
Uh?
Whoa, did you see that?
What'll we do,
Kusakai? I mean...
[NOZOMI, RIN]
...she ran right past us.
[MIO] Let's pick up
the pace and pass her!
Hey, wait!
I don't get why we're runnin'
faster all of a sudden?
We have to!
We're members of the elite class
of Setouchi Keijo
Training Academy!
And we're not about to let
some old lady on her
morning jog pass us by!
Why are they so competitive?
There she is! Look!
She glared and then went faster!
Uh-huh!
It seems like the old lady's
challenging us, doesn't it?
Sure does! Let's show
her what we can do!
No! We couldn't catch up to her!
[MIKU] What happened?
Why is everyone out of breath?
Well, uh...
Ya see, there was this
really fast old lady.
I'm afraid that
I don't understand.
[NOZOMI] She had a hat
and a towel around-- Uh!
That's her! The old
lady who beat us!
Excuse me? Who're you
calling an old lady?
[NOZOMI]
What're you doing here?
Ya think maybe she's stayin'
at the same inn as we are?
[GIRLS gasp]
Oh no, now what did she do?
It's falling!
[gasps]
Surface-to-Surface Butt Missile!
[SHIRAYUKI] Sheesh. You kids
have got a lot to learn.
Honestly, you're
inelegant and loud.
And it seems you girls
have absolutely no respect
for your elders.
[NOZOMI gasps]
I can't believe she
knocked the lumber away
without a running start!
We've been waiting for you.
This is Ms. Kyouko Shirayuki,
a pro Keijo player.
She's called the
Missile Lady of Kyoto,
and she's currently ranked
as the most popular
player in Honshu.
So that's her.
[NOZOMI]
The Shirokuma Lady of Kyoto!
Missile Lady.
Give me a break, Kobayakawa.
Dontcha think you're layin'
it on a little too thick?
[MIKU chuckles]
You ladies should feel special.
She came back to town
specifically to teach
at this training camp for you.
You came all the way
here just to train us?
Well, thank you, we're honored.
Who knew our instructor would
be an active Keijo player?
[MIKU] I did! I thought
I told you that.
No, you forgot.
I get it now.
I was wondering why we had to
come all the way here to Kyoto.
Well, I dunno about the others,
but I'm stoked to learn from
a pro player like you.
This doesn't happen every day.
It's nice to meet everyone.
Let's train hard.
[GIRLS] Right! Thank you
for teaching us, ma'am.
[NOZOMI]
She's incredible.
It took some serious
butt strength
to attack the way she did.
She's gotta be crazy strong.
I don't think I could
handle a hit from her.
Well, I'll catch you
ladies tomorrow.
[NOZOMI] Honestly, I think
everybody was in shock.
We'd never been around
an active pro before.
We had no idea they were so
much stronger than us amateurs.
Allow me to introduce you
to the three Keijo pros
you'll be training
with this camp.
Miyo Harada, A-Class player
with the Kyoto Kansai Branch.
I'm happy to say that I'll be
working with the outfighters.
It's nice to meet you all.
I'm also an A-Class player
with the Kyoto Kansai Branch.
My name is Inoue and I'll be
working with the counters.
Thank you for having me.
I introduced myself
to you yesterday.
I'm Shirayuki, an A-Class player
along with these ladies.
I'll be working
with the infighters.
[NOZOMI] Shirayuki's an
infighter, just like me!
[MIKU]
Now listen up, everyone.
I hope you understand
it's rare for amateurs
to get personal training
from active Keijo players.
Stay focused and listen closely.
You may never get a
chance like this again.
All right, it's time for
you to split into groups
and get to work!
[GIRLS]
Right!
Bye, Nozomin! You go kick
infighter butt, okay?
Will do! See ya, Non.
[NOZOMI] I can't believe I get
to train with an active pro.
I wonder if she'll
think I'm any good.
I'm gonna do my
best to impress her.
Nozomi! The infighters
are headed this way.
[gasps] Coming!
Let's get out there and
show 'em how it's done!
[SHIRAYUKI] So you're
Setouchi's elite infighters?
Nice to meet you.
We'll get started with your
specialized type training
in a minute.
First, there's something
I need to say to you
and I want you
to listen closely.
[ALL]
Hm?
There's nothing I hate
more than dishonesty.
Cheaters won't be tolerated.
If I find out that any of
you are being deceitful,
I will do everything I can to
make sure you never go pro.
Do I make myself clear?
[GIRLS]
Yes!
[NOZOMI] Man, talk about harsh!
She's hardcore!
Kaminashi, let me see
your hands, please.
[NOZOMI]
Yes, ma'am.
Don't you think your nails
are a little long, young lady?
When playing Keijo,
sometimes it's necessary
to use your arms to balance or
build momentum for an attack.
If your nails are too long,
you risk hurting yourself
and your opponent.
It's considered rude
and it's dangerous.
It never even crossed
your mind, did it?
[NOZOMI]
Ah! She's so mean!
[SHIRAYUKI]
Unacceptable!
Here, let me clip them for you.
[NOZOMI]
And now she's nice!
Wow, you're good at that.
Thanks. Remember to keep
them trimmed from now on.
Hm?
Look at your shirt, Kusakai,
the edges are all frayed!
Unacceptable! Let me
patch it up for you.
Oh. Thank you, ma'am.
[NOZOMI]
When she says "unacceptable,"
she means it's unacceptable
unless she fixes it herself.
[SHIRAYUKI]
Okay.
Now that you girls are
presentable and ready to go,
I would like to get to
know each of you better
and the best way to do
that is... with a race.
Here's what we're going to do:
One at a time you'll come up
to the Land and race me.
As I feel there is
no better way for us
to understand one another.
[NOZOMI]
It's happenin'!
It's only the first day
and I get to test my skills
against a pro!
I can't wait to show
her how strong I am!
Nozomi Kaminashi.
I'd like to thank you
for this opportunity.
I'm ready when you are, ma'am!
[gasps]
C'mon, don't you know better
than to throw your
shirt into the river?
[NOZOMI]
Uh! Oh, sorry about that.
[SHIRAYUKI] Hey, Kawai?
Would you be our time-keeper?
[HANABI]
Sure!
[NOZOMI]
She's intense.
You can tell she's
an active player,
'cause of her
commanding presence.
And her cute swimsuit, too.
Here we go!
Time to start the race!
Well, I suppose we
should get started.
Remember, no holding back.
Give me all you've got.
Yep, That's what
I was plannin' to do!
You're a fast one.
She dodged it so easily!
What about this?
[NOZOMI]
She's not retaliatin'!
I'll just have to
keep instigatin'
till ya finally strike back!
[MIO gasps]
She spun on her pivot leg
so she could attack twice!
That's crazy! Where did she
learn a combo like that?
[NOZOMI] Boobs? No way! How'd
her knockers get in my face?
She's been hit!
No. That's not the case.
Shirayuki was just standing
there when Nozomi turned around.
[NOZOMI]
Damn it! How'd she do that?
Just when I thought I was movin'
a lot faster thanks to the UTM.
It's almost as if she knew
where I was gonna move.
This is hard to watch.
She's toying with Nozomi.
One minute left!
[NOZOMI]
What is the deal?
I was attackin' with
all my strength
and I couldn't touch her.
She's not even out of breath!
So this is the difference
between an amateur and a pro.
[NOZOMI]
Fine. I won't give up yet!
I've seen that build-up.
The Vacuum Butt Cannon!
[NOZOMI] I'm determined to
go pro when I graduate!
I've gotta prove that
I'll be ready to fight
in the big leagues
in six months.
I won't let this end
without landin' a hit!
[yelps]
[NOZOMI]
I'm outta space to get momentum!
You've got amazing core
strength, yet your body's soft,
and you use your flexibility
to your advantage.
You aren't afraid to go up
against a strong opponent.
These are all
impressive qualities.
[NOZOMI] Crap! I stopped too
fast and lost my balance!
[SHIRAYUKI] And that's what
makes this such a shame.
[HANABI] No way! Only one hit?
She struck right in
the middle of her butt!
[NOZOMI]
I've never felt so much power.
She threw me off the Land
like I was a friggin' ragdoll.
[NOZOMI]
I fought hard,
and I still couldn't even get
close enough to touch her.
Active pros are tougher
than I thought.
[SHIRAYUKI] I know you're
probably disappointed,
but you need to understand
that you have a weak point.
It may be your body's
greatest flaw.
Whaddaya mean? What
kinda weak point is it?
Wait, you don't know?
You've got to be more
aware of your own body.
[gasps]
You need to know
your weaknesses
so that you can overcome them.
Believe me when I say
that's the only way
for you to become a
stronger Keijo player.
If you don't listen to your body
and figure out what its lacking,
your butt will never
be able to touch me,
or any other pro Keijo
players for that matter.
Now then, who wants
to race me next?
[NOZOMI]
I don't understand.
My body's flawed?
But how can that be?
[SAYAKA grunting]
[SAYAKA] Goodness, this thing's
even tighter than I thought.
But it makes my boobs look big.
They're not giant, but
they're bigger than normal.
You like my bosoms, boys?
They're so bouncy!
Um. No, they are not.
[SAYAKA yelps]
[NON, KAZANE]
Not at all.
[SAYAKA cries]
[NOZOMI] Next Time:
"Where the Turnips Lead!"