[NARRATOR] In the past,
gamblers have been limited
to horse, bike, boat,
and car races.
But now there's a new form
of legalized gambling
sweeping the nation.
It's called Keijo!
Players compete to be
the last girl standing
atop a floating platform
called a "Land."
The kicker? They can only
use their boobs and butts!
The question is:
Who will rule the land?
Will it be the 18-year-old
Nozomi Kaminashi?
She's one of the
many young ladies
whose search for fame
and fortune has lead them
to the world of Keijo!
And this is the story of their
journey to becoming champions!
[HITOMI]
Listen up, ladies.
Keijo begins and ends
with the buttocks!
It's the foundation of the
sport. So let's tone it!
Give me 100 figure-eights!
On the double!
[GIRLS]
One! Two! Three! Four!
Five! Six! Seven!
Eight! Nine! Ten!
[HITOMI]
Toyoguchi! Aoba! Try to keep up!
'Kay, sorry!
Now I want you to give me three
sets of 100-meter butt-walks!
Man, this is harder
than I thought!
[HITOMI] Pick up the pace!
Ten laps to go!
[GIRLS]
Yes, ma'am!
[HITOMI] Toyoguchi, Aoba!
You're falling behind!
[NON]
I'm so sorry!
[HITOMI] Okay, that wraps
up morning practice.
You better get used to it.
As long as you're in
the regular class,
you'll be doing this every
morning for the next year.
[GIRLS groan]
[HITOMI] Your training at
Setouchi isn't gonna be easy.
The reality of the situation
is one in five students
will drop out before graduation.
You're stuck with me.
That is, unless you
work hard enough
to get bumped to elite class.
We'll be grading you not only
on your physical abilities,
but your overall behavior and
general attitude as well.
So keep that in mind.
Stay strong and train
hard every day!
[NOZOMI] I can't get over
this place! It's amazin'!
If you ask for extra eggs
and rice, they'll give it to ya!
[NON] I asked for a larger
serving and I sure got it!
[SAYAKA]
Yes, I can see that.
[NOZOMI] Oh, to think,
I can start every morning
by eatin' as much rice
with egg as I want!
Talk about luxurious!
I dunno about you guys but...
...I could get used to this!
[YUKO]
Gimme a break.
If you think this is impressive,
then you should see what
they serve the elite
class for breakfast.
It looks outta this world!
[NOZOMI]
Huh?
Ah! You gotta be kiddin'!
[SAYAKA]
Why'd you have to drag me along?
[NOZOMI] It's not fair,
they get a full-out feast!
[NOZOMI gasps]
[chuckles]
[NOZOMI] They can have
ice cream for breakfast?
Ohh!
[SAYAKA] It's only the first
day and I'm already jealous.
[NOZOMI] Oh! The elite class
is so friggin' lucky!
[HITOMI]
Ten 200-meter sprints!
[GIRLS]
Yes, ma'am!
[HITOMI] C'mon, Toyoguchi
and Aoba! Move it!
Give me 20 pull-ups!
[GIRLS]
Five. Six. Seven.
[yelps]
[HITOMI]
Fifty sit-ups!
[GIRLS]
Twenty-one. Twenty-two.
[HITOMI]
Now, 100 squats!
[GIRLS]
Ninety-six. Ninety-seven.
Ninety-eight. Ninety-nine.
One hundred!
[NOZOMI groans]
[NOZOMI]
I'm so over physical trainin'.
[MIKU] In the world of
Keijo we have a saying:
"Know not thy rump,
never shalt thou triumph"!
It's not enough to train
your bodacious behind.
If you want to excel at Keijo,
you have to understand
the science behind it.
A science called "Asstronomy."
Breasts and buttocks are very
intricate subjects of study.
Has anyone ever
noticed Westerners
tend to have higher
and firmer derrieres?
Well, there's a reason for that.
It's because their pelvis
is tilted differently.
Most Japanese pelvises
tilt backwards,
however, Westerners'
have a forward tilt
that causes their
tushies to sit higher.
Bet you never knew
that, did you?
Learning the mechanics behind it
all will help you train in a way
that best suits
your body's needs.
[NOZOMI]
They're already on the Land!
Aw, man, the elite
class is so lucky!
Sit back down!
[MIKU] ...and learn to
attack with precision.
Like this!
Did you get all of that,
Miss Kaminashi?
[NOZOMI groans]
Yes, ma'am.
[HITOMI] You've got two
more laps. Pick up the pace!
I don't think I've
got two more in me!
Today's training was super hard!
You can say that again.
You don't seem
too phased, Miyata.
I didn't think it
was all that bad.
But we're gonna train
this hard every day
for the rest of the year.
I'm well aware and I'm ready
for it. I want to go pro.
Yeah, me too!
I should prob'ly start
paying more attention
to the pro players.
There was a chick I saw
at Nishinomiya Stadium
who attacked with her butt and--
Bam! She won!
I wish I could remember
that player's name.
It's a weird one.
Somethin', somethin' Kyoto.
If she was using big,
flashy moves,
maybe it was Shinonome!
Nah, I know that's not it.
Aw, c'mon, brain, she was
the somethin' Lady of Kyoto.
[NON]
Uhh... Shirokuma?
[NOZOMI]
Yeah, that's it! Shirokuma!
Ya heard of her, Aoba?
She's awesome!
The Shirokuma Lady of Kyoto!
[HITOMI]
Training begins now!
[NOZOMI yelps]
[HITOMI]
Now sprint!
[GIRLS]
Yes, ma'am!
[NAGISA]
Begin!
[GIRLS]
Yes, ma'am!
[NOZOMI]
This sucks.
I wanna practice on the Land.
C'mon, let's go.
We're going to be late.
I don't wanna.
You can't make me!
[NOZOMI sighs]
I think we should get
to practice on the Land
at least once, don't you?
[HITOMI]
Fifty-meter dash!
Look at me! Number one!
Well, yeah! Only because
your tire fell off!
It did?
Okay, Miyata. You're the
ref so what's your call?
She's disqualified. Execute her.
[NON screams]
[HITOMI] That's enough, room
309! Quit messin' around!
Keijo-Style Tire
Rolling. Let's go!
[yells
[GIRL E]
Are you blind?
[MIKU] Looks like we've
got a strong group
of newbies this year, don't we?
[HITOMI] Yeah, I think they're
ready for the next step.
Gather round!
Today you'll be learning a
technique called the hip toss.
It's a type of training that
utilizes a beach ball.
Your roommates
will form a circle
and you must toss the ball to
each other without dropping it.
What makes it challenging is
you can only use your butt.
No breasts.
Your goal's 30 tosses.
The team who comes in
last will get a penalty,
so do your best!
[GIRLS]
Yes, ma'am!
Whoa! Cool!
We're finally gettin' into
some real Keijo trainin'!
[NOZOMI]
Hey, Aoba, you comin'?
Gals, I say we forget about 30
and shoot for a hundred
consecutive tosses!
Okay, here goes.
Got it!
I'm headed that way!
[BOTH gasp]
Sorry about that!
Oh, no, that was my fault.
Well, let's give it
another try, you guys.
[BOTH gasp]
Oh, man, this ain't
workin' at all.
Hey, keep in mind which
way the wind is blowin'!
--[SAYAKA] Roger!
--[NON] Will do!
Alrighty, heads up!
[NOZOMI]
I got it!
Crap, the wind changed
direction again!
There's no stoppin' me!
[gasps]
[NOZOMI, KAZANE groan]
Ow. Sorry. Are you okay?
Whoa, Aoba. I had no idea
you were so stacked.
Hey, don't be mad!
If it weren't for your
massive jugs, I'd be hurtin'.
I'm just glad I ran into you
instead of Miyata.
[SAYAKA]
'Scuse me?!
Who'd've thought bouncing
a beach ball off our hineys
would be this difficult?
Yeah, no kidding. This is
harder than I thought it'd be.
Let's try directing each
other towards the ball.
--[NOZOMI] Cool with me!
--[NON] Sounds good!
[NOZOMI] Miyata, the wind's
blowing it over your way!
I see it!
[NOZOMI]
More to the left!
Okay, got it!
[SAYAKA] I'm so sorry.
I didn't see you there!
Toyoguchi!
I'm ready!
[NOZOMI]
Move up! You need to get closer!
Whoa, that's too much! Get back!
Aw, c'mon! You didn't
have to go that far!
Yeah, I see it now!
Uh-oh!
Oh goodness gracious.
Sorry I got in your way, Aoba.
[NOZOMI] It's all good,
ladies. Let's try again!
[NON] It's moving
towards you, Nozomin!
[SAYAKA]
Keep going straight ahead!
[NON]
Ah mah lawd!
That darn thang's
gone cattywampus,
you'd better skedaddle!
I have no clue what you're
tryin' to say to me.
Oh, dagnabbit, it's fixin'
ta fall right behind ya!
To the left, Nozomi!
[NOZOMI]
All right, I got this!
[NOZOMI sighs]
It's impossible to understand
Non's accent. Right?
[NON] Oh, dear, we were
so close this round.
[NOZOMI]
We'll get there.
[HITOMI]
Time's up!
We didn't even
complete one toss.
[HITOMI] Looks like
room 309 came in last.
You girls will stay after class
and give me 100 figure-eights.
[ALL groan]
[GIRLS] Ninety-eight.
Ninety-nine. One hundred!
[HITOMI] Good work.
You're done, ladies. Dismissed.
It's over!
We can't let this happen
again tomorrow, you guys!
Do you think we should
try changing places?
That's not the problem.
We could change
positions all day long
and it wouldn't
make any difference.
Well then, what is it?
We have to work together.
It's the only way to get
through the challenge.
You need to communicate
with us. Please, Aoba.
[NOZOMI]
It's all about teamwork?
Of course.
That's what today's hip
toss exercise was testing.
I'm all for that,
but not in Keijo.
[NOZOMI] Yeah, I've always
thought of it as more
of a solo sport.
It might seem that way.
But behind the scenes there's
more teamwork than you'd think.
For example, I've heard
pro Keijo players
who work for the same agency
bounce ideas off one another.
They discuss new tactics before
they try them out on the Land.
Makes sense, if you ask me.
There are a lot of
different factors
you need to take into account
when you're coming up with
your attack strategies.
It would help to have another
player's input on stuff.
It's important we communicate
with each other
in order to get a hip
toss combo going!
[SAYAKA] That's the
only way it'll happen.
[HITOMI] Today I'll be
testing you and your team
on your hip toss.
You've got 30 minutes to
practice and then we'll begin.
[GIRLS]
Yes, ma'am!
I've got a special treat for the
team who comes in first place.
They'll get to taste the most
delicious gelato in Awaji.
[GIRLS gasp]
Why's that special?
And what in the heck
is gelato, anyway?
The elite class was eating it
for breakfast, remember?
Oh, that stuff!
Now I'm all fired up!
That fancy ice cream
is goin' in my face!
[SAYAKA clears throat]
I have an idea that just
might make that happen.
[NOZOMI] Ya think we
should pick a leader?
[SAYAKA]
Yes.
We need one person acting
as everyone's eyes
and giving out the orders.
That's a great idea!
[NON] Okay, then I nominate
Miyata for team leader!
It's up to you, Aoba.
Are you cool with that?
Get it, Toyoguchi!
[NON]
Will do!
[SAYAKA]
A little more to the right! Uh.
Oh no! The wind blew
it the other way!
No, that's too far left!
Move, uh. Um.
[NON yelps]
That was all my fault.
My orders were awful!
Funny.
I thought it was
coming straight to me,
but it went to Aoba instead!
Heads up, Nozomi!
Got my eye on it!
[SAYAKA]
Move back a little bit!
Okay, now to the left?
Wait, I was wrong!
Ugh, I'm the worst leader ever.
It's no big deal.
It's just weird that it ended
up going right to Aoba again.
[NOZOMI] Aoba's footprints...
Could it be?
[NOZOMI]
Let's try it again!
[NON] Watch out, Miyata!
It's coming in behind you!
[SAYAKA]
Roger!
[NOZOMI]
It's just as I thought.
[NOZOMI gasps]
[SAYAKA]
I've got it!
[NON]
Careful, Miyata! Move forward!
[BOTH gasp]
[NOZOMI] Somehow, she knows
where the ball's gonna land!
[NOZOMI]
How are you doing that?
You have to be our
team leader, Aoba!
[KAZANE gasps]
[SAYAKA]
You honestly think she's been
reading the wind
this whole time?
Is that possible?
[NON]
Sounds farfetched.
There's no other explanation.
Everywhere the ball goes,
she's always right behind it.
Well, I get why you
want her to be leader,
but she doesn't
want the job.
I don't blame her.
It's a lot of responsibility.
[NON] What're we gonna do?
We need a leader!
Don't worry,
'cause I've got an idea!
[HITOMI] So far our highest
combo is 35 consecutive tosses.
Let's move on to our
last team: Room 309.
[GIRLS]
Yes, ma'am!
Hey, Aoba!
Just do what you've
been doin', 'kay?
[HITOMI]
Begin!
[NOZOMI]
Here we go!
[NOZOMI gasps]
Miyata the ball's headed
five diagonal meters
to the left of Aoba!
Gotcha!
That's one!
This way! It's two meters
to your right, Non!
[NON]
Okie dokie!
This is awesome.
You know exactly where
the ball's gonna land.
I'm simply reading your signals.
And two!
[gasps]
[NOZOMI]
Your ponytail.
Whenever you notice the wind
changing, your ponytail moves!
[NOZOMI]
Three!
As long as I can see your hair,
it's not hard to figure out
where the ball's going.
Wow, that's really smart.
[NOZOMI]
Miyata!
It's five meters to your right
and three meters behind ya!
[SAYAKA]
I'm on it!
[thud]
[NOZOMI]
Your turn, Non!
It's four meters to your left
and then take a small step back!
[NON]
Yeppers!
'Kay, Aoba! You're up!
[KAZANE gasps]
Looks like you've got
the hang of it now!
This makes 35!
[GIRL F] They've matched
the highest team combo!
How're they doin' it?
Ready, Non? It's two
diagonal meters to your left!
[gasps]
[NON]
I'm headed that way!
[gasps]
[KAZANE]
No!
[GIRLS gasp]
You're wrong! Kaminashi!
It's 15 meters back and two
meters to the left! Trust me!
[BOTH gasp]
[NOZOMI] I've been waiting for
you to finally speak up, Aoba!
That's 36, baby!
She was waiting on me
to say somethin'?
Great work today.
[NON] Thank you! We couldn't
have done it without ya!
[NOZOMI] We did it, guys!
We're the top team!
Whoops, didn't mean
to knock you over!
Guess you're the
clumsy one not me!
I don't know my own strength!
[NOZOMI]
What?
You were embarrassed of
your Hiroshima accent?
[KAZANE]
Yeah, it may seem silly,
but on the first day you said--
Wow, Non, your accent's the
funniest thing I've ever heard!
[NOZOMI laughs]
You stopped talking because you
thought she'd make fun of you?
In other words,
this is all your fault.
[NOZOMI]
Guess I should watch what I say.
I'm really sorry, y'all.
[NOZOMI] If anyone should
apologize it's me!
Sorry. Um, "y'all."
[SAYAKA] You can be so
insensitive sometimes.
[NOZOMI] It's finally
time for Land class!
I've been waiting for this day!
It feels like it's been forever
since I've been on a Land!
[NOZOMI grunts]
Uh. What do you
think you're doing?
Nothing. I just
noticed your butt.
It looked so firm
I had to touch it.
Whoa, what's going on over here?
That sounded naughty!
What? I meant it's more
muscular than before!
You can't help but notice
everyone's curves
in these swimsuits 'cause
these things are skin tight!
Seriously!
They've helped confirm
what I already suspected.
I knew you had a nice rack,
but didn't know
how nice till today.
[KAZANE gasps]
Stop it! Don't be creepy!
[NOZOMI] There's no need
for you to be embarrassed!
So what cup size are you? A "D"?
Not quite that big, huh?
Lemme guess, a "C"!
Ah-ha! We have the
same cup size!
But... I never.
I know.
Nozomin's having a
conversation with her ponytail!
I don't understand why
Aoba would be embarrassed
by her breasts when
they're a "C" cup.
[HITOMI] I'd like to welcome
you to your first Land class.
We're going to be
starting things off
with a mock race
against the teachers.
We'll be using a basic Land.
Each team of four students
will compete with one teacher.
Four against one, huh?
I like those odds.
[HITOMI] We'll evaluate
your Keijo ability
by going cheek-to-cheek
with you on the Land.
Don't worry about
holding back.
I want you to give me
everything you've got.
[HITOMI yells]
Ms. Hokuto's really strong!
I still can't believe
they're gonna make us
play against a teacher!
If we gotta do it,
then we might as well win.
[NAGISA]
Okay. Up next is room 309.
[ALL gasp]
[NOZOMI]
Why'd we get the seal?
You know she can
hear you, right?
Ms. Ujibe may not look it now,
but she used to be
quite the prize queen!
[SAYAKA]
Nagisa Ujibe.
She was a top player
in Keijo's early days.
Her remarkable beauty
and her playful tactics
earned her the nickname
the "Alluring Siren."
[grunts]
[NOZOMI]
You're kidding.
What're you mumbling
about over there?
C'mon, let's get started!
[GIRLS]
Yes, ma'am!
[NOZOMI]
Don't let her intimidate ya.
We gotta stick to the plan!
[NOZOMI]
I'll go first!
Crap, she didn't even budge!
Fine then!
Let's work together to show her
just how powerful
our team can be!
Look! Nozomi's out on the land!
[NAGISA]
Hm.
You're trying to copy
the Butt Gatling
technique, aren't ya?
She dodged all of my attacks!
Watch out!
Now's my chance to strike
while they've got
her distracted!
[NOZOMI]
If I can gain momentum,
then maybe, just maybe,
it'll make my attack
even stronger!
Interesting. Bring
it on, kiddo. Huh?
Take this!
She dodged it!
[gasps]
[ALL gasp]
[ALL scream]
[NON] What in the world
just happened?!
No way. That was...
...a Vacuum Butt Cannon!
Uh. Sorry?
[NON] Nozomin. Why're you
wearing that crazy get-up?
[NOZOMI] All I know
is it's called a UTM.
What's that stand for?
Ujibe's Training Maillot.
You look dumb.
Hey, don't say that.
[NOZOMI]
Next time: "Vacuum Butt Cannon!"