If you ask me, you're way too
talented for the regular class.
[ALL gasp]
Hello, ladies. I'm the fastest
outfighter in Western Japan.
Rin Rokudo.
Nice to meet ya.
I seriously doubt that you're
the fastest, but whatever.
[RIN] The others are lame and
none of them even come close
to being in my league
as an outfighter.
There's an event coming that's
going to shake things up.
It'll be fun for us, but maybe
not so much for your roommates.
An event, huh?
[RIN]
Yep, the class-change race!
[MIKU]
Five seconds to start.
Four. Three. Two. One.
This'll be easy.
Huh?
[SAYAKA]
You're going down!
[RIN chuckles]
How'd she dodge my attack?
And she did it at
the very last second!
She's faster than I thought.
[RIN laughs]
I'll admit that you
caught me off guard.
So you really wanna
do this, huh?
You know, rushing me at the
beginning of the race like that
wasn't a very smart move.
Let's not forget I'm
the fastest outfighter
in all of Western Japan.
[SAYAKA]
You keep saying that,
but I think we all know
better than to believe it.
Oh?
Well then, if I'm not the
fastest, then tell me who is.
Isn't it obvious? That'd be me.
Ha! Hold up, you seriously
think you're the fastest?
Wow. Looks like I'm gonna
have to teach you a lesson.
You're nowhere near my level.
[NARRATOR] In the past,
gamblers have been limited
to horse, bike, boat,
and car races.
but now there's a new form
of legalized gambling
sweeping the nation.
It's called Keijo!
Players compete to be
the last girl standing
atop a floating platform
called a "Land."
The kicker? They can only
use their boobs and butts!
The question is:
Who will rule the Land?
Will it be the 18-year-old
Nozomi Kaminashi?
She's one of the
many young ladies
whose search for fame
and fortune has lead them
to the world of Keijo!
And this is the story of their
journey to becoming champions!
Whoa, that's a lot of
power for a single attack.
Actually, she hit
them ten times.
[HARUMI]
What the--?
[HARUMI, KURURU yelp]
[MIKU] Konishi and Nemoto
overboard! Loser!
Did you see that? The Land
tilted over to one side!
Well yeah, that's how
the Seesaw Land works.
It's a hemisphere shape so it
has a weak center of gravity
which makes it sway more
than the other types.
This thing's intense, huh?
Much better. Now it's
your turn to go down!
Wow.
I thought you were all talk,
but somehow you're
keepin' up with me.
It just means that I'll have
to move a little faster!
[chuckles]
[gasps]
[RIN] Havin' a hard
time now, aren't ya?
That's crazy!
How's she movin' so fast?
She's good. She's quick
and she's a great fighter.
[SAYAKA yelps]
Hang on, Miyata!
This is bad. She's been pushed
to the end of the Land.
One false move and
she's going overboard!
[RIN]
Talk about boring.
You claim to be the fastest
and that's all you've got?
Well, this was great,
but I'm over it.
You should do some
speed training
before you fight me again.
Thanks for playin',
but it's game over for you!
Wow, you're gullible.
[RIN gasps]
She was faking!
She pretended to be off-balance
so I'd go in for the big finish.
You'll never be the fastest
with that giant ego
slowing you down.
[SAYAKA]
Triple-Thrust Hurricane Attack!
I don't know how you just upped
your speed all of a sudden.
Unless, you were
pretending to be slow
so you could set up your attack!
How humiliating.
I can't believe she
was holding back on me.
How could I be so stupid?
I didn't notice her plan to
trick me 'cause I was cocky!
[NON] My goodness, it looks like
Rokudou's awfully frustrated.
[NOZOMI] Good! That means
Miyata hit a nerve!
She could win this, you guys!
[MIO]
Don't be so sure.
She got a decent attack in,
but only because Rin-rin
had her guard down.
It was a solid effort, but it
didn't do nearly enough damage
to take her out of the race.
I went at her with
everything I've got,
and I still couldn't land
a single hit on her.
Even her reactions are fast.
I'm not falling for
your tricks again.
So don't even
bother here on out!
It's over for ya.
I'm gonna make sure
I beat you this time!
Let's go! Butt Gatling!
[SAYAKA]
Don't count me out yet!
[yells]
She's repelling all
of Rin-rin's attacks!
They're both moving so fast.
It's a battle of sheer will!
I never thought I'd find a girl
fast enough to keep up with me,
much less in the regular class.
I guess I've gotta accept it.
I've finally found someone
worthy of fighting.
There's no denyin'
you're quick and strong.
That said, it's still not enough
for me to feel threatened.
They're really going at it!
Yeah, it's one big
blur of butts!
[chuckles]
What happened?
It looked like Miyata
stopped movin' for a second.
[RIN yells]
She's strong!
Do you think maybe
Miyata's hurt
and that's why she's getting
pushed to the edge?
No. She's fine.
But her breathing's off.
It looks like she's
oxygen deprived!
Just fall already!
It takes a lot of concentration
to move so quickly.
She prob'ly holds her breath
when she's attacking.
She's not breathing
while she fights?
If that's true,
then shouldn't Rokudou also
be oxygen-deprived right now?
'Cause she hasn't
slowed down at all.
[HANABI] There's more to
Rin-rin than just her speed.
[NON]
What do you mean by that?
Well, she happens to have an
extremely large lung capacity.
[NOZOMI]
Why's that matter?
[HANABI] Miyata and Rin-rin
are basically even
when it comes to their
speed and reflexes.
But there's one area where
Rin-rin has an advantage.
And that's lung capacity.
[HANABI] Their Butt
Gatlings may be equal,
but Rin-rin has
more "ammunition"
because she's never
gasping for air.
[RIN] I can take a hundred
shots with a single breath!
Bet you can't do that, can ya?!
[yelps]
It's been fun, but this is it.
Oh no, she's gonna
lose the race!
Thirty seconds.
No, she won't.
How do you know?
She's worked hard.
Miyata has been training
every day. She won't give up.
She's been looking
for a technique
that'll make her the
fastest Keijo player.
And now she's finally found it.
[SAYAKA]
Three. Two. One.
W-Acceleration. Activate!
Her swimsuit!
She wedged it up her butt!
Do you think that's
gonna help you?
How the hell did
she get over here?
Whoa. She's fast!
What was that? It's like her
ass disappeared for a sec.
But she couldn't pull that off.
She's not fast enough!
[SAYAKA]
Too slow.
[RIN]
No way!
My goodness!
What's going on?
Why's she so fast now?
I don't get it. All she did
was give herself a wedgie!
Pulling her swimsuit up like
that cuts down on resistance,
thereby increasing her
hips' range of motion.
Sorry, I'm not
followin', Kazane.
Our swimsuits are thin,
but they still exert
pressure and constrain us.
The faster you move, the
more that pressure builds up
and it eventually starts
to slow you down.
But when you pull your suit up,
it instantly reduces
the pressure
and allows you to gain speed.
[RIN]
Damn it! She's too fast!
That's it. You're done.
You won't defeat me!
Just watch me!
I'm going to win this race!
[RIN]
I may not have a big butt
or giant boobs
like everybody else,
but I've got super speed
and that's enough!
But how? We both lunged
at the same time.
[gasps]
[SAYAKA]
You're quick,
but you'll have to settle for
being the second fastest
outfighter in Western
Japan from now on.
[RIN screams]
[MIKU]
Rokudou overboard. Loser!
[MIKU] Class-change race, group
one, winner: Sayaka Miyata.
[NOZOMI] Hell yeah!
I knew you could do it!
I can't believe
Rin-rin was defeated!
[MIO laughs]
She kinda deserved it.
[gasps]
Oh no, she fell!
What's the matter,
Miyata? Are you okay?
I'm fine, just wiped.
[RIN]
Think I figured it out.
You knew you couldn't keep
that crazy speed up for long.
That's why you waited
to use your new technique
until the last 30
seconds of the match.
Gotta admit, I'm
seriously impressed
you came up with that
all on your own.
I can't call myself
the fastest outfighter
in Western Japan anymore.
Guess I'll hafta be "the fastest
outfighter in Western Japan,
excluding Sayaka
Miyata" for a while.
How very humble.
I'm pretty bummed that I lost,
but I'm glad I got to
race against you today.
We should train together
and then try this again.
I think it'd be fun, don't you?
Fair warning though,
next time we race,
I'm totally kicking your butt.
[rubber stretching]
[SAYAKA groaning]
Ow, that hurts! Be careful.
[SAYAKA]
I'm really sore.
She worked her muscles so hard,
they're completely stiff.
[SAYAKA]
Please don't push so hard.
[NON] Are you okay?
I wish I could help somehow.
[NOZOMI] I feel bad for Miyata.
She's so beat up.
I guess it's the only
way to win though.
You gotta hit the
elite class-ers
with everything you've got.
[screams]
[KAZANE] All right,
you're back to normal!
[MIKU] Group two, five
minutes until your race.
Oh. It looks like it's my turn
to get out there and fight.
Okay!
I'm gonna follow in
Miyata's footsteps and win!
Non Toyoguchi is about to
show 'em a real Keijo battle!
[NON]
I talked a big game poolside,
but now I'm scared to death.
[NANA yells]
I'm advancing to the
elite class, not you!
[NON]
What should I do?
I feel kinda silly 'cause
I'm just standing here.
Oh, poor Non. Think
she's gonna be okay?
[SAYAKA grunts]
This race is as good as done!
All it will take is one hit!
We'll see about that.
Namu!
Ow!
[NOZOMI]
That's crazy!
The attacking player
was sent flying!
[ATSUKO]
The Ass of Vajra.
When I tighten my butt, it
becomes as strong as steel
and easily blocks any attack.
You see, my ass is
the ultimate shield,
deflecting whatever may hit it.
And thus, it can become...
the ultimate weapon!
[MIKU] Ooshima and Gotsui
are overboard. Loser!
[whimpering]
You must be terrified,
little girl.
In that case, let me go ahead
and put you out of your misery.
Stay away from her, Non!
One hit from her and you'll
be knocked overboard!
[ATSUKO] Finishing move:
Steel Lance Ass Attack!
[screams]
Is she okay?
Uh! Her butt is like
a marshmallow!
[ATSUKO yelps]
Her ass... it's so squishy!
[MIKU] Yoshida. Namuamidabuts--!
Uh, I mean, overboard.
Loser!
Uh?
What just happened?
[MIKU] Class-change race, group
two, winner: Non Toyoguchi.
So she absorbed
Yoshida's attack
and then shot it
right back at her?
Exactly, Toyoguchi's
got soft buns
that can assassinate
enemy asses.
[NOZOMI]
I guess whatever works for ya.
I did it, you guys!
I actually won the race!
[NOZOMI, NON]
Yay!
Dunno why you're celebrating,
you just got lucky!
[NON] That's not true! You
take that back right now!
[NOZOMI]
Chill out, Non, you won.
Does it really matter
whether it was luck or not?
Of all people, I thought you'd
have a little more faith in me.
Hmph.
[MIKU]
Members of group three,
please make your
way to the front.
Time for me to get out there.
I'm gonna make you
guys proud. I promise!
Follow my lead and
kick their heineys!
You can do it, Aoba.
Yeah, go get 'em, tiger!
[MIKU] Group three is going to
compete atop a Pole-Type Land.
[KAZANE]
This'll be tough.
I'm going up against
the strongest player
in the elite class.
[MIO]
Well, here we go.
Fun! I can't wait to start.
I get to compete against
all these lovely ladies.
It's almost as if
I have my own harem.
No stress, girl!
You've got this thing!
[RIN] This race'll
be over in seconds.
Yeah, Mio won't have any
trouble taking those three out.
Kazane's a lot stronger
than you think she is.
Kusakai got first place
in the entrance exams.
Doesn't matter if it's a
practice match or what,
she never loses.
[HANABI]
If anyone's a Keijo prodigy,
it's most definitely
Mio Kusakai.
[NON] Don't listen to them.
Aoba can win this!
[MIKU]
Five seconds.
Four. Three. Two. One.
[bell rings]
Ooh!
Did she just charge
in by herself?
Yeah, that was crazy!
You caught me by surprise.
I wasn't expecting anyone
to come rushing at me
as soon as the bell rang.
What'll I do with you?
I know, when this race is over,
how would you like
to come home with me?
[yells]
[MIO laughs]
Your bravery's a turn on,
but you'd better be careful.
You don't wanna be too reckless.
If you wanna sink me,
your best bet is teaming up
with the other hotties
and working together
to take me down.
She's got a point!
You can't beat her alone!
Team up with the others!
Don't worry, guys.
Aoba's got it under control.
[yells]
Your friends sure
are distracting.
Don't they know how hard this is
for a shy little cutie like you?
Oh no, she's hurt!
[KAZANE coughs]
[MIO]
Done already?
I was hoping you'd last longer
so that we could have some fun.
Now, Shimada.
This is our chance!
[gasps]
How did she get
in my blind spot?
Okay, you're up next, Horiuchi!
[MOMO]
Roger!
That wallflower is giving
the others orders?
Sorry, she got away from me!
No problem! I expected her
to dodge in that direction.
Wait a second, how'd you figure
out which way I would dodge?
I know all about you, your
moves, and your techniques.
Everything.
Thanks to my Scanning Hand!
You got that info
from your hand?
[KAZANE]
That's right.
All I have to do
is touch someone
and then my right
hand reads them.
It gives me their condition
and even their habits.
For example, you tend
to favor your left leg
because it's much more
flexible than your right one.
So when you're attacked,
you always dodge right.
Get it now?
Ooh.
I don't remember letting you use
this "Scanning Hand" of yours.
I used it on everyone in
school when I gave massages.
[NON] See? Now you'll be able
to get data on everybody!
Seriously?
We were kinda skeptical
when she told us all of this
before the race.
But we decided we might as
well play along with her
'cause we wanna beat you.
I know every move you're gonna
make before you even make it.
There's no way that
you're gonna win.
Wow.
[MOMO, AI yell]
Sheesh.
[KAZANE] You can run all you
want, but I'll still catch you.
There's no escaping me.
Good job! Way to go, Kazane!
Well, what did I tell you?
I had no doubt she was
gonna pull out a win today.
Aren't you clever?
I must admit,
teaming up against me
and then blocking my every
move is a brilliant strategy.
[laughing]
What in the--?
Why'd she change her
stance like that?
She's standing there...
swaying her boobs.
[MIO]
Fantastic!
You're an even better Keijo
player than I imagined, Aoba.
[laughing]
What is she doing?
She keeps laughing.
[laughing]
[KAZANE] What in the
world did she do to me?
I'm stuck!
I can't move a muscle!
[SAYAKA] I don't like this.
Something seems off.
[NOZOMI] They're just starin'
at each other. What's goin' on?
[KAZANE]
I can't... even speak.
No. It can't be.
Sorry, girlfriend.
[KAZANE]
No way!
She used... Titty Hypnosis?
[MIKU] Aoba, Shimada,
and Horiuchi are overboard.
Loser!
She went overboard!
[HITOMI] Medics! Get those
girls out of the pool right now!
Hurry!
[MIKU] Class-change race, group
three, winner: Mio Kusakai.
[NOZOMI]
But I don't understand.
How did she lose?
[NON]
I have no clue.
I mean, Aoba and the
others had her cornered.
[SAYAKA]
Whatever she did, it must be why
she's the elite class's
number one student.
[NOZOMI]
I just wish we knew what it was.
[SAYAKA] Listen, I know
you're worried about Aoba,
but you need to focus.
Yeah, it's gonna be tough.
Kotone Fujisaki.
[NOZOMI] I don't know anything
about her techniques,
but I do know that no
matter what she tries...
[NOZOMI]
...I'm gonna sink her!
[NOZOM panting]
How's she doin' that?
Her booty is comin' after me!
[roar]
[NOZOMI]
No!
[thud]
[NOZOMI]
Next Time: "Full-Auto Cerberus!"