[ANNOUNCER 8A]
Ladies and gentlemen,
it's time for the spectacular
battle royale featuring
the future stars of Keijo.
The East-West War!
[NAMI screaming]
[NAMI screams]
The Nipple Full Shoulder Throw!
[ANNOUNCER 8A] The first
round goes to the West
after a stunning upset
over the reigning champions!
It's all because of that seal.
[AYAKO]
All right, ladies.
Setouchi's heavy hitters
fought in the first race.
And, unfortunately,
we lost before we had
the opportunity
to prove ourselves.
But let's take a look
at their next team.
Are you okay?
You look pale.
What's got you so worked up?
[KAZANE]
Don't worry, I'll be fine.
I'm just nervous
'cause I've never raced
in front of a crowd this big.
My stomach's
full of butterflies.
You should try meditating.
It'll help calm you down.
Yeah! Pull yourself
together, Kazane!
Our race is going
to start in a few minutes!
Hey, Non, do you know
your outfit's on backwards?
You're right!
What the heck's wrong with me?
[USAGI]
You've gotta be kidding me.
Listen up, we can't blow this.
We need to go out there
and kick some serious butt.
We owe it to our teammates...
and to my beloved Kusakai
who won the first race for us.
The fact that she used so many
of her tantalizing techniques.
My love! I swear you're
a goddess walking on Earth!
Chill out, Tsukishita!
You'll hurt yourself!
[USAGI]
Ah, my goddess, Kusakai!
That's who we're up against?
They're not much of a challenge.
For real.
This race'll be over fast.
I was hoping we'd at least
have a little fun.
I'd say this one is in the bag.
You're taking on
their second string.
As long as you stay
focused and play hard,
we're practically
guaranteed a win.
Let's show them who's strongest!
[ALL]
Right!
[ANNOUNCER 8A] All right,
ladies and gentlemen,
the second race of the
East-West War is about to begin!
Now that they've
won the first race,
let's see if Setouchi can
keep up their winning streak.
Will the underdogs
score a second victory
against their rivals?
Or will the invincible
Suruga strike back
and prove they still rule?
We're about to find out, folks!
For the second round
of the East-West War,
our players will be
racing on... a Flight Land!
There are two linked aircraft
floating in the pool.
Everyone's dying to know which
team will soar to victory!
And now, it's time
to introduce our players!
First up, we have
the team from Suruga.
[CROWD cheering]
[MALE CROWD MEMBER 10A]
Let's do this!
[ANNOUNCER 8A] Her favorite
hobby is fortune-telling
and her mystical fairies
can't get enough
of her butt! Ayase Kurogiri!
I can hear my fairies
whispering louder than
ever before and their message
is crystal clear.
[ANNOUNCER 8A]
Here's a player who knows how
to turn up the heat. She sets
her fans' hearts ablaze
with her Hot Butt! Kei Higuchi!
I'm fired up now!
[ANNOUNCER 8A] Next, we have
the girl with the best rhythm
at Suruga. She's known
as the Battle Dancer!
Mai Itoeda!
And last but not least,
we have the heiress
to the Hououin Conglomerate,
the "Black Beast" herself!
Sanae Hououin!
Whoa, everyone's cheering
so loud it's almost deafening!
And now, the Setouchi players
will make their entrance.
[ATSUKO]
Namu amida butsu .
[ANNOUNCER 8A] One minute
until the race! Stand by!
What? Oh no! It won't come off!
What's the matter?
I think the button's broken!
I keep pushing but
it's not doing anything.
Come on. Please work.
[NON]
Hold on, lemme give it a try.
Let's see, what if I do this?
[KAZANE]
Uuh!
It ripped off--aah!
[NON, KAZANE coughing]
[MALE CROWD MEMBER 10B] Are they
Keijo players or clowns?
With the way they're acting,
you'd think they'd
never raced before.
It's like our instructor said,
they're second-string,
they're not meant to win.
It kinda sucks
we have to race 'em, huh?
[ANNOUNCER 8A]
The race will start in five.
Four. Three. Two. One!
[bell rings]
Don't tell me
you're still nervous?
Fine, I'll go then!
Tsukishita!
[ANNOUNCER 8A] Tsukishita from
Setouchi is making her move!
Ooh. She's got some guts,
doesn't she?
I can't believe she's
rushing in without a tactic.
Right? This'll be
over in a flash.
[MAYA]
Hmm.
Do you want a fight,
little girl?
[USAGI yells]
In that case, well...
I'll give you one!
Guard Waltz!
No way! How in the hell
did she deflect all my attacks?
Your tempo's too slow.
[USAGI screams]
[MAI]
Battle Waltz!
What the--?! Her techniques
look more like dance moves!
Let's see if you can
keep up with me
when the tempo starts
getting faster!
[BOTH]
Tsukishita!
We gotta help her!
I think we should try
to get behind 'em
and then pincer 'em!
Okay!
They're doomed.
They'd better save their friend
while they still can.
They never should've split up.
If they go one-on-one against
our girls it's over.
Where do you think
you're going?
[ANNOUNCER 8A]
Kurogiri has stopped Yoshida
right in her tracks!
Get outta the way!
Rin. Pyo. To. Sha. Kai.
Jin. Retsu. Zai. Zen!
Ass of Vajra: Improved!
[AYASE]
I call upon my fairy friends.
Grant me your power
so that I may transcend!
I shall now summon you
forth with a chant!
Come out of your fairy bower,
come upon this golden hour,
come to me, I beg you please.
Fairies dancing on the breeze!
Fairy Butt!
[ATSUKO grunts]
That's impossible!
Her booty's stronger than
the Ass of Vajra.
It can split rocks!
You think she's
actually got fairy power?
Oh, please.
There's no such thing.
She simply hypnotized herself.
Whoa, you can do that?
[SAYAKA] Yes. By convincing
herself the fairies are real,
she can tap into the power
that's controlled
by her subconscious mind.
[ATSUKO groaning]
First Tsukishita gets
in trouble, and now Yoshida?
[KEI] Yep, that's right!
And you two are next!
You're going down!
Soft Buns!
[shrieks]
She rubbed Toyoguchi's butt
and it caught fire!
Why don'tcha go ahead
and jump in the pool
if the heat's too much for you?
Get too close to my Hot Butt
and you're bound
to get burned.
We can take her
if we work together!
Just follow my lead!
[NON]
What'll we do now?
Guess we're on our own.
[ANNOUNCER 8A] It's not
looking good for Setouchi!
Suruga's got the team split up!
There we go. Let's see them
try to get outta this.
The only reason
they won the last round
is because they were able to
use their numbers against us.
But now that we've
got them one-on-one,
they're sure to lose the race.
[KAZANE grunts]
[ANNOUNCER 8A] Aoba from
Setouchi has been pushed
to the edge by Hououin!
[NON screams]
[ATSUKO groans]
[NON, ATSUKO grunting]
[NON panting]
Told ya they wouldn't last long.
I'm surprised
they're still standing.
They're weak and their
teamwork's all over the place.
That sucks.
--They were doing so well.
--It's over for Setouchi.
We should prob'ly
put you out of your misery.
You're going down
with a giant splash!
It's time!
The ones makin' the splash...
[ALL]
...will be you!
[ANNOUNCER 8A]
Amazing! Did ya catch that?
Setouchi pulled
off a brilliant ruse
knocking the
Suruga ladies off balance!
What? There's no way!
[BOTH gasp]
[ANNOUNCER 8B] Higuchi and
Itoeda have gone overboard.
Loser!
Oh, hell yeah!
That was amazin' teamwork!
Whoever came up with the plan
to stomp the linked
parts of the plane
and flip 'em up like a seesaw
is a friggin' genius!
You know what
I find most impressive?
The fact that they
lured their opponents
to those positions
without them even noticing.
It's kinda funny
when you think about it.
Suruga thought they were
cornering our teammates.
But little did they know,
they were the ones
who were being cornered.
It was a brilliant strategy.
[AYAKO grunts] I can't believe
my girls fell right into
the enemy's trap.
They're stronger individually,
but Setouchi's
teamwork is fierce.
We can win. I know it.
[ANNOUNCER 8A] Thanks to
their impressive strategy,
Setouchi now has
a four-on-two advantage!
Way to go, Aoba.
Your plan worked like a charm.
Well, it's all
thanks to you guys.
[SANAE clapping]
[SANAE] Nice work. Not only did
you lure us into your trap,
you then used the Flight Land's
layout against us.
And now you have the advantage,
in number anyway.
Miss Kazane Aoba, was it?
You are quite the tactician.
Here I was going to
hold back on you ladies.
But it looks like
I can go all out now.
I'm with you. Why hold back
when we can have fun?
Is that supposed to scare us?
'Cause it doesn't. Not one bit.
Think you can take me? Bring it!
Be careful, Yoshida,
she's tough.
She's ruthless and
she hits hard. Real hard.
[ATSUKO] Then I'll go
at her with full power!
Huuuuu--aaah!
[ALL gasp]
[BOTH gasp]
[ANNOUNCER 8B] Yoshida has
gone overboard! Loser!
[USAGI]
Oh crap. We're screwed.
[KAZANE] And I thought
she hit hard before.
One down, three to go.
Your turn.
I'm not strong enough
to take her head-on.
If I use my speed then she
can't keep up with me!
Ah! That's impossible!
I thought I could outrun her,
but she's as fast as me!
[yells]
[NON]
I got ya!
You okay? That was a close one.
Yeah, thanks for savin' me!
She's not messin' around.
How're they s'posed to race
someone with power and speed?
That's a deadly combination,
if you ask me!
[SANAE grunts]
Aah!
Where is all that
power coming from?
Hey, Kazane.
Ya think maybe we should
try to pull back and regroup?
[AYASE]
Like I'd let that happen!
I beseech thee,
oh fairy friends,
grant me your power. Hip power!
Shoot! The fairy
girl's here, too!
[ANNOUNCER 8A]
You'd think Setouchi would have
the upper hand since
it's three-against-two,
but it looks like Suruga
has them cornered!
The West's players
are mediocre at best.
Now that the gloves are off,
we can play at full capacity.
Those girls are in
a for a rude awakening.
We're trapped. What'll we do?
We gotta move
or they'll sink us.
Okay, I've got a plan
so listen up.
It might sound crazy
but I need for the two of you
to team up on the fairy girl.
[BOTH gasp]
You heard me right.
Her fairy power isn't real.
The truth is, it's hypnosis.
That's where she's
getting her power,
but it's taking
a toll on her body.
It'll wear her down eventually.
Try to stick it out until then.
If that's what you want us
to do, but you do realize
you'll have to fight the
super-strong chick alone.
--[KAZANE] Mm.
--[NON, USAGI gasp]
If we don't do something
we're gonna lose.
I know it's risky but I think
it's a risk worth taking.
Luckily, we know
our enemy's weakness.
If we attack it,
we have a chance
to turn this thing around.
But you don't
stand a chance against--
[NON]
Understood.
We'll take fairy girl.
With two of us it shouldn't
take long to wear her down.
'Kay, Kazane, stay strong.
We'll be back
after we've sunk her.
Uuuh!
[ANNOUNCER 8A]
And Setouchi makes their move!
Thanks, you guys.
Don't let me down.
I'm counting on you.
[SANAE]
Huh. I see what you're doing.
You've got them double-teaming
Kurogiri to exhaust her.
It didn't take you
long to figure her out.
Her "fairies" don't
fool you. Good plan.
But there's one problem.
Now that your friends
are busy you have to fight me.
And I'm not sure
you can do that.
[KAZANE] You haven't even
seen what I can do yet.
So don't act like
you've already beat me!
Oh, come on! Don't tell me
that's all ya got!
[SANAE] Wait, why's she's
not pulling her butt back?
[KAZANE] I'm gonna borrow
a move, Kaminashi!
Meteor Hip!
But how? A player
her size shouldn't be able
to use that technique!
Yeah! Way to use my move!
[SANAE]
Uugh!
[ANNOUNCER 8A] That was
a fierce attack from Aoba!
It's got Hououin reeling!
I know I'm not the strongest.
You're probably
a better athlete than me.
But still,
I'm not losing this race!
[MIKU] Here's the thing,
you've been given a gift
that you need to use.
Your Scanning Hand technique
has so much potential.
[KAZANE]
Uh?
I've talked it over
with everyone here
and they said they're more
than happy to help you out.
[ALL]
Hi!
We've all been
training like crazy.
Our butts are
a lot stronger now!
[MIO] You might as well
benefit from our hard work.
[ALL] Go ahead, Aoba!
Touch our butts again!
Thank you, all! I promise
that I'll make you proud!
You think we're one-on-one,
but in reality, you're facing
all of Setouchi's students!
I need your help, Murata.
Reflection Butt!
Damn it! She moved
just like I did,
as if I was looking in a mirror.
[KAZANE]
All right, Rokudo. Hydra Butt!
Another technique?
Now Kawai! Hammer Hip!
I don't get how
one person could have
so many butt techniques!
[gasps]
[SANAE] Her right hand. Every
time she moves it like that,
her attack style changes.
[SANAE gasps]
It can't be!
[KAZANE] You get it now?
All I have to do
is touch someone's behind
with my right hand.
And I have access to
all their butt techniques.
Basically, I can steal them
and put them in my arsenal.
Gate of Bootylon!
I tried to warn you;
you're not just fighting me,
you're taking on
all my teammates, too!
[ALL holler]
[SANAE] Heh. Ridiculous.
You're just copying others.
Everyone knows fakes don't even
come close to the original.
You're nothing but a fraud!
[KAZANE]
Kusakai! Derringer Hip!
Yeah, maybe my attacks
are just copies,
but if I use them wisely
I'll find the perfect one
to send you overboard!
Eh! Why, you--
I finally understand the secret
behind all your power!
It comes from twisting
and releasing your body
but you're only
using your lower half!
[grunts]
That's why it's easier
to counter your attacks!
C'mon, Sanae,
don't let her beat you.
Interesting.
I see there's more to you
than just being
a copycat. However...
...my twisting techniques
aren't limited to my butt!
[gasps]
Uh-oh. What now?
Perky Pile Piper!
[KAZANE] She's drilling
into my nipples! Aah!
[NOZOMI]
Kazane!
[ANNOUNCER 8A] That had to hurt!
Hououin's drill-like boob attack
has thrown Aoba
to the front of the Land!
[KAZANE gasps]
[ANNOUNCER 8A] The poor girl's
in pretty bad shape.
She's trying
to stay on her feet
but it looks like
she's having a hard time!
Ooh. I was certain that move
would send you overboard.
I guess I'll just have
to try again.
She's so powerful.
Another hit like that
and I'm done for.
Here it goes! Thanks for
the fun fight Kazane Aoba!
Haa! One-Point-Six-Kilo
Boob Napalm!
Are you okay?
Yeah, I am now!
But you were fighting Kurogiri!
Does that mean...? Oh no!
[USAGI, AYASE panting]
[AYASE] Why can't you
stay still for one minute?
[SANAE] Her Fairy Butt's
been deactivated!
Now it's back to her regular,
flabby backside!
[ANNOUNCER 8A]
Has Suruga fallen for another
of Setouchi's tricks?
Kurogiri's keister has
gone from buns of steel
to flat and flabby!
It looks just like
a newborn baby's!
I don't have a flabby butt!
What? You dodged that?
Damn straight! I've got you now!
My legs are spent.
The rest is up to you two!
I'm takin' fairy girl
overboard with me!
[AYASE]
No!
[CROWD cheering]
[ANNOUNCER 8B] Kurogiri and
Tsukishita have gone overboard!
Loser!
We're the last two.
[SANAE] Hah.
Things just got interesting.
Perky Pile Piper!
Uh!
[SANAE] My boobs
aren't spinning anymore!
You idiots! Don't you
realize blocking my boobs
with your butts is only
delaying the inevitable?
That's what you think, lady!
You have no idea
how strong we are
when we work together!
Our bond is sacred!
We're friends, roommates,
and the best partners!
To hell with both of you!
We've almost got her!
[ANNOUNCER 8A]
These ladies aren't giving up
without a fight! At this rate,
we'll end up with a tie!
There ya go! Show her what
you're made of, you guys!
How is this happening?
[ALL grunt]
Had enough? You may be
stronger than us individually,
but not as a team. We will win,
and there's nothing
that you can do to stop us.
We can do anything together!
We'll have to see about that!
Watch out! It's a feint!
[NON screams]
[ANNOUNCER 8A] Toyoguchi goes
flying through the air!
Toyoguchi!
I'll admit you got us with that
sneak attack you pulled.
But still, I won't fall
for that again. You hear me?
Your tricks won't work on
a top of the line competitor!
[NON]
Gotta reach it!
[ANNOUNCER 8B] Toyoguchi has
gone overboard. Loser!
[SANAE] Damn it, I lost my grip
on one of my boobs!
You might've
beaten me if you had
worked with your team.
I truly respect my teammates.
I wouldn't have gotten this far
if it wasn't for them.
They've taught me
the importance of teamwork.
They're the ones
who've given me this chance.
I'll win it for them!
Boob Dunk!
[yells]
[KAZANE screams]
[SANAE yells]
[ANNOUNCER 8A] That ringing
bell means we've reached
the end of the race!
Aoba and Hououin knocked
each other off the Land
and went overboard
at the same time!
The question is
will the judges call a tie?
Oh. Looks like they're
going to review the video.
We did it! She hit
the water before Kazane!
I don't think so.
Take a closer look at it.
She lost.
[ANNOUNCER 8A]
The loser is Aoba!
The second race of the
East-West War goes to...
...Suruga!
Well, this is a new one!
The air pressure coming
from Hououin's boob
kept her above water
just long enough to win!
It's official, folks.
Suruga is our winner!
That's the end
of the second round,
ladies and gentlemen.
Gotta give it to Setouchi--
they may be the underdog,
but they're giving it
their all. What a race!
This one is sure to go down
in the Keijo history books!
[HIKARI]
Do you ladies like magic?
'Cause I've got
a supreme illusion
that I'm simply
dying to show you!
For real? You're gonna
do a trick for us?
Yeah. Watch this.
I'll unleash
my Bust Power! Haaa!
[RIN]
No way!
[NOZOMI] Next time: "The Castle
of the Final Match!!!!"