[knock, knock]
[SAYAKA]
It's me.
Please, Dad,
if you would just
hear me out then maybe--
[SAYAKA'S FATHER] We've already
had this conversation.
I told you. No daughter of mine
will dedicate her life to Keijo.
I've heard enough
of your nonsense.
But that's what I want to do--
You have the talent to become
a world-class
judo champion someday.
You should continue
on that path.
I've said all I care
to say on the matter.
All I've ever wanted to do
is become a Keijo player!
Why don't you understand, Dad?
[SAYAKA'S FATHER] You're the
one who doesn't understand!
What're you going to do--
run from judo?
No, that's not it.
The truth is I--
[CROWD cheering]
[ANNOUNCER 8A]
Five seconds. Four. Three.
You had a judo career
and you ditched it.
You just ran away. Ha!
[SAYAKA]
I didn't run from anything!
I'm here because I want to be!
[ANNOUNCER 8A]
Ladies and gentlemen,
the first race of the
East-West War has begun!
It looks like Miyata's the
first player to make a move!
She's headed straight
for Nanase from Suruga!
I doubt that she'll make it
to me without falling.
Finishing move!
God Hip Impact!
[ANNOUNCER 8A] A meteor has
rained down from the heavens!
Ogre Hanayama's on the scene!
Oh no!
Careful, Miyata,
don't rush in recklessly.
Yeah, thanks for the save.
[ANNOUNCER 8A]
Whoa, that was a close call!
Luckily, Fujisaki saved
Miyata's ass with her own!
Huh. I gotta admit,
that was a great attack.
How do we beat her, Murata?
I dunno. She's pretty big.
It'll be difficult
to shake off her--
[gasps]
[KAHO] Mission accomplished.
Capture complete.
Hey, let go!
Now requesting attack.
[MARI gasps]
[AKARI] Ha-ha! Behold my
asstronomical technique!
Assteroid... Afterglow!
[MARI]
Twinkle, twinkle, little star.
How I wonder butt you are.
[MARI groans]
[ANNOUNCER 8B] Mari Murata
is overboard! Loser!
[BOTH]
Yay.
[ANNOUNCER 8A]
Suruga scores the first sink
of the East-West War!
We're only thirty seconds
into this race
and they've already got a major
advantage over Setouchi!
I can't believe
I'm watching this.
[MALE CROWD MEMBER 9A]
Aw c'mon, don't let 'em
defeat ya again this year!
Get it together, Setouchi.
You can do it!
Woo! Show 'em how it's done!
Akari! Kaho!
Now hurry and take out
the rest of their team!
[NAMI] You gals might've
had a chance against us
if you'd devoted
your training to Keijo.
[NAMI] But you wasted years
training in other sports
and then dropped 'em
like a hot potato.
Not only are we more skilled
than you Westerners,
we're more adaptable
and way classier.
I hate to break it
to you but you plebs
just aren't on our level.
Poor things.
You must live in a dream world.
You've got nothing on us!
If you don't
believe me then I guess
we'll just have to show you!
What the--?
Here they come.
--[CERBERUS roars]
--Oh crap!
--[MIO, SAYAKA grunt]
--[SAKI] No no no no no!
[SAYAKA, KOTONE, MIO]
Setouchi-Style
Combination Attack.
Triple Assembled Attack!
[SAKI grunts]
[ANNOUNCER 8B]
Hanayama goes overboard. Loser!
Setouchi's combination
took down the Ogre!
[NOZOMI]
Way to go!
[ANNOUNCER 8A] Looks like
we're in for one hell of a race!
[BOTH] Mm! We'll get you
back for Hanayama!
I've always dreamed
of having a threesome
with twins, you know!
--[CERBERUS roars]
--Let's go, Cerbie!
[KOTONE gasps]
Uh-oh! You're still standing?
You should've fallen by now!
No!
[SAYAKA] Fujisaki!
W-Acceleration. Activate!
Thanks, Miyata.
I was almost a goner.
What kinda weird
technique was that?
It seems that young lady
increased her speed
by expanding her lower
body's range of motion.
[SAYAKA]
Wedgie release.
[SAYAKA groans]
What's with my legs?
I can't move 'em!
[NAMI]
I thought that might happen.
I mean, using
that much acceleration
is bound to take its toll
on your body eventually.
Now into the water
you go, ya loser!
[CERBERUS roars]
[KOTONE]
Butt-Fang Stab!
I'm not letting you get past me!
You wanna butt in, huh?
I'll just sink you first!
Careful!
[laughs]
Come and get me!
But you should know
that your attacks aren't going
to work against me anymore.
'Cause now I know...
how your ass tastes.
You're disgusting.
I'm putting an end
to this right now!
[CERBERUS roars]
[KOTONE groans]
What did she do?
I don't get what happened.
Me either, I thought that
Fujisaki attacked her.
This Nanase chick's tough.
That was one heck of a counter.
That's not what I saw.
She didn't counter,
she just took the hit!
I know, but she's
being selective.
She's only taking hits
from the weak parts
of Fujisaki's caboose.
[KAZANE, NON, NOZOMI gasp]
[KOTONE] There's something
weird about her.
She's got a creepy aura.
It almost feels as if she's
feeling me up with her stare!
[KOTONE whimpers]
[NAMI]
Okay, playtime's over.
Now it's time for me
to eat your ath up.
[KOTONE]
How's she doing that?
She keeps hitting
my body's weak spots.
Those Setouchi girls
don't stand a chance.
Their skills can't compare
to Nanase's synesthesia.
What's "synesthesia"?
I've never heard of it before.
You'd know if you
had paid attention
to your teammates
during training.
How should I put this?
Basically, it's when one of
your senses
is linked with another.
Nanase can distinguish
between her opponent's
strong and weak spots just by
looking at their body.
She sees each area
as a different color,
almost like thermography.
Your butt's turning
yellow because you can't
put any strength into it.
Looks like it's almost
time for me to eat.
I simply can't wait to dig in!
I'm gonna devour
your tender flesh
with my fork and knife!
Merci c'était très bon !
[gasps]
How dare you!
You'll pay for that, Kusakai!
You're pushing yourself
too hard, Fujisaki.
Try not to let this crazy
broad get to ya, okay?
Ya gotta be more malleable
with your attacks.
Get what I'm sayin'?
Uh. Yeah, I think so.
[MIO]
Sorry for the wait!
Where were we,
my little twinsies?
Don't underestimate us!
We're stronger than you think!
[AKARI, KAHO gasp]
What did you do?
Oh, did you like that?
You cutie?
Well, in that case, I've got
somethin' you'll like even more!
[KAHO moans]
[AKARI moans]
Told ya you'd like it.
Now let me hear you
moan, honies!
I call this move
the Queen's Bounty!
[AKARI, KAHO moan]
[ANNOUNCER 8A]
Setouchi's Kusakai has rendered
Suruga's Akari
and Kaho powerless!
And it looks like the twins are
actually enjoying her attack!
I've never seen such
a terrifying technique!
Disgusting! I wouldn't
call that a "technique."
I guess she's too much for the
twins to handle on their own.
I'll go and help them
as soon as I can.
But first, I need to
get rid of this weakling!
[SAYAKA]
Crap! I can't run!
[KOTONE] Tit-Fang Stab! I'm your
opponent, not her, got it?
[NAMI]
You're wasting your time!
You're not strong enough
to take me on,
especially not
in such close quarters!
Now get outta my way, or else!
[SAYAKA]
Fujisaki!
What, do you think
your friends can save you?
You're a sitting duck,
Miss "former judo
representative of Japan"!
[SAYAKA grunts]
Did you not
hear me the first time?
I'm your opponent, Nanase!
Leave her alone!
[CERBERUS roars]
I've had it!
I won't let you sink
any more of my teammates!
Fujisaki.
Setouchi taught me what
it means to be part of a team.
I hated training. Now I find
it fun because of them!
That's why... I'll do
everything within my power
to protect my allies!
We've worked so hard.
We're not losing this year!
I'm determined...
...to defeat you!
--[CERBERUS roars]
--[KOTONE groans]
Dream on, girl.
You couldn't possibly beat me.
My synesthesia will
make sure that never happens.
You see...
[grunts]
[NAMI] It helps me
predict your every move!
[ANNOUNCER 8B]
Fujisaki has fallen! Loser!
Are you all right?
[KOTONE]
Stay back!
If you touch me,
you'll be disqualified.
[SAYAKA gasps]
Sorry, Miyata.
I tried my best,
but it just wasn't good enough.
So, please...
[sobs]
...win it for us. For Setouchi.
[ANNOUNCER 8A]
Nanase's unrelenting attacks
finally wore Fujisaki out!
We're down to three against two!
I'm afraid it's not looking
good for Setouchi, folks.
Why put yourself
through this misery?
You can keep trying to hang on
but I'm still gonna sink you.
So much for Cerberus.
He may be called
the hellhound
but he was more like
a hound in the pound.
Aw, there's no need to be sad.
You'll be reunited soon.
'Cause I'm going to
make sure that you go down
just like your doggy friend.
Okay, are you
finished talking trash?
Let's get this over with!
You've got one serious butt
kicking comin' right at you!
Well, well. Look who's
made a full recovery.
[SAYAKA] Thank you, Fujisaki.
You sacrificed yourself
to buy me time. I promise,
I'll make the most of it!
W-Acceleration...
What is she doing?
She hiked it up even higher!
[SAYAKA]
...Full Purge!
W-Acceleration:
Full Purge Activate!
She pulled it so far.
She ripped her swimsuit bottoms!
[gasps]
Your power's pretty neat.
I'll bet knowing your opponent's
moves make things easy for you.
Whoa!
[NAMI screaming]
Unless your opponent
is too fast for you to see.
[NAMI grunts]
Just you wait, I--
[groaning]
[NAMI]
So fast!
I will defeat you.
Consider it payback
for what you did to Fujisaki.
[NAMI]
Let's see you try!
Aaaugh! Damn it!
She's too fast.
I can't predict her moves
if I can't see her.
But--
Oh no! She stopped Miyata!
[NAMI] It doesn't matter
how fast you are,
as long as I keep
you in close range
you won't be able
to build up any speed!
[SAYAKA yells]
No way!
Down you go!
[MALE CROWD MEMBER 9C]
Did you see that?
[MALE CROWD MEMBER 9D]
Nice work, Setouchi!
Look at her go!
See, dear?
Our little girl's a star.
Aren't you proud?
[SAYAKA yells]
I can't go down like this!
What should I do?
[SAYAKA] C'mon, you can do it.
Just a little bit more!
[SAYAKA gasps]
[SAYAKA]
My legs.
[ANNOUNCER 8A] Just when
thing's were looking up,
Miyata from Setouchi is injured!
Don't give up now!
C'mon, you almost had her!
Just a little bit farther!
You can do it, Miyata!
Yeah, we believe in you!
[CROWD cheering]
[CROWD] Mi-ya-ta!
Mi-ya-ta! Mi-ya-ta! Mi-ya-ta!
Sayaka.
[SAYAKA]
Move! Move, dammit!
I hope you had fun
while you were winning
but now it's my turn.
[KAHO]
Please stop!
This is so embarrassing!
We're begging you!
[MIO chuckles]
I'm not stopping
till I've completely broken
down your faux personas.
[KAHO] No, cut it out! I can't
take much more of this!
No one's ever had
this effect on me! Oh no!
I love hearing
your cries of pleasure!
Now let's try this:
Hip Nip Shock!
[BOTH moan]
Oh yeah. I had a feeling
that you'd like this move,
you naughty little twinsies.
[BOTH moan]
[NAMI]
Talk about a one trick pony.
You're worthless
without your speed.
[SAYAKA grunts]
But don't you worry. I promise
this will all be over soon.
[SAYAKA groans]
[NAMI]
Barbare je suis pleine !
Y'know, it's funny--
just a few minutes ago
you were bragging about
how fast you are
and now you can't even move!
I bet you regret wasting
all those years practicing judo,
'cause you're no match
for a dedicated
Keijo player like me.
I've been going to
Keijo camps since I was
in elementary school!
I hated milk when I was a kid
but I drank it anyway
to make my boobs bigger!
Unlike you, I've remained
faithful to my sport!
I could never throw away
all my years of hard work
but that's exactly what you did
when you dropped out of judo!
[SAYAKA groans]
[SAYAKA'S FATHER]
You're willing to throw it away?
Your years of experience--
not to mention your hard work.
You want to give up
all your achievements
just so you can try
your hand at another sport?
[SAYAKA] I may be new at this,
but I work hard and train hard.
Lemme show you!
I thought she was
completely worn out
but she's still going strong!
Who cares if you've trained
for Keijo your whole life?
That doesn't make you
better than me.
Sayaka.
Sure I have to prove myself,
prob'ly more than anyone else.
But I'll do it because
I've always dreamed of
standing on the Land!
[gasps, giggles]
[SAYAKA] I'm not here because
I "ran away from judo."
No, I'm here
because I love Keijo!
I'm finally living my dream!
Why's she fondling her boobs?
She's really goin' at 'em, huh?
She can't do too much
with 'em. They're A-cups!
You think you can attack me with
those mosquito bites of yours?
Gimme a break!
Remember, I've got
the power of synesthesia
which means I can see
right through your attacks!
[NAMI gasps]
Her entire body's relaxed.
Don't tell me she's
gonna throw the match?
[gasps]
Her tits! They're the
only part of her that's red!
I don't understand why she's
focusing all her energy there.
[SAYAKA yells]
Holy friggin' crap,
her nips are beaming!
[SAYAKA yelling]
She caught my swimsuit
on her erect nipple!
[yells]
Oh, my! But isn't that move...
No, It can't be.
[SAYAKA'S FATHER] Judo relies
heavily on the lower body
so we need to
build those muscles, too.
You can use your rear end to
knock your opponent off balance.
C'mon, use your butt!
[SAYAKA'S FATHER]
Sayaka.
[SAYAKA] You missed out
training in only Keijo
'cause I've learned all kinds
of judo techniques
that've made me
a better athlete!
You think you're
so much better than me?
Well, I'm about
to prove you wrong!
[NAMI screams]
The Nipple Full
Shoulder Throw!
[ANNOUNCER 8A]
Nanase is down!
[SAYAKA'S FATHER]
Hm!
[KAHO, AKARI scream]
[ANNOUNCER 8B] Akari and Kaho
Fuyuzora have gone overboard!
Loser!
Nami Nanase has fallen! Loser!
--[bell ringing]
--[CROWD cheering]
[ANNOUNCER 8A] That's the end
of our first race!
[ANNOUNCER 8A]
The first round goes to the West
after a stunning upset
over the reigning champs!
That's right,
ladies and gentlemen,
Setouchi's won the first race
of the East-West War!
Hell yeah!
They did it! We won!
Miyata was amazing
out there, wasn't she?
[AYAKO]
We were mistaken about them.
Who'd've thought Sayaka Miyata
would become such
an asset to their team?
It's all because of that seal.
[CROWD cheering]
[SAYAKA'S FATHER]
Good work today, Sayaka!
[SAYAKA]
You're here. Mom! Dad!
[NON]
Welcome back, Team One!
You guys absolutely killed it!
[KAZANE]
Yeah, and you looked so cool!
[HANABI] That'll show 'em
not to mess with Setouchi!
[USAGI] My beloved Kusakai,
you were amazing!
[NAGISA]
I'm very proud of you, ladies.
That was an incredible race.
[ALL]
Thanks!
Your wedgie acceleration
was freaking insane!
You kicked ass out there!
What's wrong?
You're not hurt, are you?
My dad's here.
He came to watch me.
[gasps]
My parents are in the stands.
Both of them, my mom and dad.
But that's a good thing,
don't cha think?
Well, yeah. I'm just
kinda confused 'cause
I didn't tell them about
the East-West War.
When you put it like that,
I guess it is a little weird.
Then again, maybe not.
Parents are always
watching their kids.
You really think so?
I'd like that.
I do, which means we
need to work even harder!
Gotta make sure our parents
have a reason to cheer us on!
I'm all for it! I really
wish I'd had the chance
to win a gold medal in judo.
But I know that
I'll make it up to them
when I become
a Keijo prize queen.
Now wait one minute.
Oh, I know! I can
buy them a massage chair
that's made out of pure gold!
Yeah, that'd be nice.
Um, I dunno
about that, Miyata.
Right, a gold massage
chair wouldn't be comfy.
No, if anybody'll be
a prize queen, it'll be me!
You've gotta be kidding me!
Let's be real here,
I've got a much better shot
at it than you do!
[NOZOMI] Whatever!
You ain't got nothin' on me!
When I become a prize queen
my parents are getting
a Harley, a Benz, a Cessna,
and a golden massage chair.
[SAYAKA] Uh! You can't just
steal my idea! That's so rude!
Told ya the West's players
are strong this year.
I gotta admit, they were great.
Lots of talent.
Miyata was awesome.
She'd make a good
cover story, huh?
Yeah! But I think we
should hold off on that decision
until we've seen what the rest
of Setouchi's team can do.
[SAYAKA'S FATHER]
She was amazing out there.
I don't think I've ever
seen her so driven.
She's a completely
different person
than the judo champion I raised.
[SAYAKA'S MOM]
But she has the same smile.
That's true.
I'm glad that you've finally
found where you belong, Sayaka.
[SANAE] My twisting
techniques are unstoppable.
And they're not
limited to my butt!
[gasps]
Perky Pile-Piper!
[NOZOMI] Next time: "The Second
East-West War Race!!!!"