[NARRATOR] In the past,
gamblers have been limited
to horse, bike,
boat, and car races.
But now there's a new form
of legalized gambling
sweeping the nation.
It's called Keijo!
Players compete
to be the last girl standing
atop a floating platform
called a "Land."
The kicker? They can only
use their boobs and butts!
The question is:
who will rule the Land?
Will it be the 18 year old
Nozomi Kaminashi?
She's one of
the many young ladies
whose search
for fame and fortune
has lead them
to the world of Keijo!
And this is the story
of their journey
to becoming champions!
Maya! Dodge it!
[MAYA]
I'm sorry, but I can't.
I've fought so hard
to earn everyone's respect.
If I were to dodge her attack,
I'm afraid I would lose it all.
And things would go back
to the way they were.
And then...
I'll be all alone again.
No!
[NOZOMI] I landed a perfect hit
with my Vacuum Butt Cannon!
That should've blown her away
but she didn't even budge!
[KAYA] Poor little Maya.
This is a bad habit of hers.
She works so hard
she ends up in tears.
You really wore her out.
That's why I offered
to take over for her.
[NOZOMI]
What?
[NOZOMI groans]
[ANNOUNCER 8A] Kaminashi's lucky
Rokudou was there to catch her!
That was quite a hit
from Sakashiro!
She could barely
stand a second ago!
It's like she's a
completely different player!
[CROWD cheering]
Are you okay?
Uh-huh. I'm fine,
just a little bruised.
[groans]
[KAYA yawns]
I've been asleep for so long.
I wasn't expecting
to wake up to this.
We're all beat up. Poor Maya
must've had some trouble.
"Poor Maya"?
What the heck
is she talkin' about?
Hold up. Just what do you
think you're doing, Kaya?
This is no time
for you to take over.
You gotta get permission
from the instructor
if you wanna fight them.
[HANABI] Who's "Kaya"? Wasn't
her name Maya a second ago?
[TAE]
Yeah, you're right.
She's the girl who
was fighting you before.
But this is a completely
different person altogether.
Maya's got this other
person living inside her.
And she's Suruga's number one
player: Kaya Sakashiro.
Let me get this straight;
you're saying she's got
two personalities?
But how is that even possible?
Well, I don't know the science
behind it or anything,
but apparently,
Maya was mistreated
by adults when she was a kid.
So now whenever she feels
like she's in danger,
she switches personalities.
I guess it's a coping
mechanism or something.
If you only played
as well as you blabber.
They've heard enough, big gal.
Why don't you sit this one out.
[TAE]
Aaah!
[ANNOUNCER 8B] Yokosugi has
gone overboard! Loser!
[ANNOUNCER 8A]
Ooh! This is a first, folks!
Yokosugi from Suruga
was knocked overboard
by her own teammate!
What is Sakashiro thinking?
What is Maya doing?
I don't think that's Maya.
It's Kaya! But what
is she doing out there?
Bring it!
Please forgive me. I realize
what I'm doing is rude.
Normally, I wouldn't dare
to interrupt your battle,
but these are
special circumstances.
She's far too dangerous
for you to take on alone.
So I'll use my breasts to help!
Now! Draw Boobs!
Quickdraw Gazongas!
[KAYA]
Bare-Breasted Catch.
She caught my boob in hers! Aah!
How dare you? Butt Gatling!
[RIN]
What the--? Aah!
[KAYA]
Bust Vise!
Hey, let go of her!
[KAYA] It's pretty pathetic
that two of our best players
were taken out
by weaklings like you.
That means I'm left to do
all the dirty work.
Just so you know,
I'll do whatever it takes
in order to protect poor Maya.
She's more brutal than before.
Ever since she
switched personalities.
This Kaya girl
is a serious threat!
Let go of her!
Heart Breaker!
[KAYA groans]
All right, Kawai!
Nice use of your
trademark critical hit!
Hurry and strike
before she snaps out of it.
Draw Boob--
That didn't hurt one bit!
It'll take a lot more
than that to stop me!
[RIN groans]
[RIN]
Kogatana!
[ANNOUNCER 8B] Kogatana has
gone overboard. Loser!
[ANNOUNCER 8A]
We've lost another player;
you know what that means!
The Castle Land sinks again!
[NOZOMI] Every time it sinks
we get less playin' area.
[KAYA] You're the one
who made Maya cry, aren't you?
Bad move. If there's
one thing I hate, it's bullies.
Nipple Ripple Madness!
Huh? What did she do?
[groaning]
What's happenin' to me?
From what I could tell,
all she did was
smack her boobs together.
But everythin's lookin'
distorted now.
--What happened?
--She okay?
[KAYA]
Take this!
[NOZOMI]
Damn it.
[KAYA]
And this! And this!
And this! And this! And that!
[panting]
[KAYA] Well, well,
isn't that impressive?
You're still hanging in there.
You know, you don't have
to go through all this pain.
I mean, wouldn't it
be a lot easier
to just jump in the pool?
Heh. Yeah, probably,
but I'm not one to take
the easy way out--
not when I've got a challenge.
Look, I don't have time
to deal with
your little temper
tantrum right now.
How 'bout you bring back
my number one target?
I've got a butt kickin' for her.
Oh really?
You can't do this alone,
Nozomi. Let us help.
Okay, fine.
--Let's attack her together!
--Here we go!
Now you're in big trouble.
How dare you treat me
like Maya's opening act!
[NOZOMI, RIN, HANABI groan]
[NOZOMI groaning]
She's got so much power!
[ANNOUNCER 8A] Incredible!
Setouchi's ganged up
on Sakashiro
three-against-one
and they still
can't touch Suruga's best!
[NOZOMI] The only way we
can beat her is if we hit her
with somethin'
that's even stronger
than the techniques
she's already usin'.
The thing is,
that's easier said than done.
I don't know what to do!
I'm about to
take you down, Setouchi.
You good?
Yeah, just sore.
Hey, what're you doin'?
[HANABI] She's too strong.
We can't keep hitting her
with the same old attacks.
We'll have to take some risks
if we wanna beat her.
[NOZOMI]
Eh?
[HANABI]
It's up to you now, Nozomi!
All you need is Rackupressure!
How're your
beamin' nips gonna help?
[KAYA]
What're you doing?
I can tell you two
are up to something!
Stay away!
Okay, so this
might sting a little.
Deal with it. Ready?
Tit Spirit!
[NOZOMI screams]
[RIN groans]
[ANNOUNCER 8B]
Rokudou has fallen! Loser!
[KAYA] You really think
that's gonna keep me away?
Here's payback for Rin-rin!
Man, these Setouchi girls
are beyond annoying.
I wish they--wha--
[ANNOUNCER 8A] Two more
players are outta the game!
It's time for the Castle Land
to sink again, folks!
[NON gasps]
Oh, no!
[NOZOMI] Thank you,
Kawai and Rokudou.
I promise I won't let you down.
You're up against me now.
Playtime's over!
[KAYA] I don't know what your
friend did, but it won't work.
One silly costume change and
you think you can defeat me?
Twin Peaks Roaring Bullet!
But that was a direct hit!
[KAYA]
Spiked Bust!
She overpowered Kaya?
No way!
Holy cow! I didn't
know what happened
but Nozomin's rejuvenated!
Yes, Kawai gave her
Rackupressure.
It increases
one's athletic ability
by speeding up regeneration and
releasing large amounts
of adrenaline.
Kaminashi's now able to use
100% of her full power.
You think you're tough?
I'll show you!
--Not again!
--That's bad!
It didn't work! But why?
It can't be.
She's bouncing her boobs
to nullify my
Nipple Ripple Madness?
[NOZOMI grunts]
Butt Flash!
[gasps]
Shoryucans!
Meteor Hip!
There's more
where that came from!
You ain't seen nothin' yet!
Sure you can handle it?
You don't scare me!
[NOZOMI yells]
Ugh! Her attacks
are so powerful now.
Why're you still
hidin' from me? C'mon, Maya.
Let's settle this
once and for all!
Forget it!
[NOZOMI] Come out and fight me!
Don't waste this opportunity!
Let's make this a race
we can be proud of, Maya!
If nothing else, do it
for your love of the sport!
I'm sure you love Keijo
just as much as I do.
If you don't come out and fight
you're gonna regret it.
Not only are you
lettin' yourself down,
but your teammates
and your instructor, too!
[MAYA gasps]
Would you shut up?
I've heard enough!
You don't know what it's like.
If she loses, she won't have
anything left to fight for.
And she'll be all alone again.
I won't let that happen to her!
But, Maya!
[MAYA] I'm sorry, Kaya.
I know that you're only
trying to look out for me.
But... I want to do this myself.
Please, Maya!
I wanna race with you!
Come out of hiding!
The Vacuum Butt Cannon!
How many can she do?
[bellows]
You wanted to
fight me so badly,
well then, here you go!
This'll show ya!
It's Maya!
Glad to see you're back.
Now, why don't we
pick up where we left off?
Come and get me!
What're you gonna do, Nozomi?
Do you even have a plan?
You can't use
the same move again.
Actually, she can.
While her Vacuum Butt
Canon is strong,
she's hasn't reached
full power yet.
That being said,
I have a feeling we're
about to see it happen.
[NOZOMI]
I can't keep firin' these off.
This'll have to be the
last one. In that case...
I'll put everything
I've got into this one blow!
I gotta make it count!
[ANNOUNCER 8A] The clock is
winding down on round three!
Will Suruga win their eleventh
straight East-West War?
Or will Setouchi become
the new champions?
We're about to find out,
ladies and gentlemen!
Hold on to your hats, 'cause
it's gonna be a bumpy ride!
Is Maya seriously
gonna go head-on with her?
Impossible! She's in
no shape for that now!
[MAYA] I hope you
can forgive me, Mom.
I'm sorry. The last thing
I wanna do is disappoint you.
But I can't keep
running away. Not now.
I'm going to do everything
that I can to win this for you!
Here I come!
Get ready for Heaven and Hell!
All-Out Vacuum Butt Cannon!
Get her!
[NOZOMI] She's takin' the hit
with just her left breast?
This hurts! It feels like my
boob's about to be ripped off!
But I've gotta stay strong!
If I use the shape of my breast
to alter her butt's trajectory
at the last second,
maybe I can--
[NOZOMI gasps]
[ANNOUNCER 8A]
Sakashiro deflected
the Vacuum Butt Cannon!
She did what?
The curvature and elasticity
of her breast killed its power!
[MAYA yells]
Now Kaminashi!
[NOZOMI]
I ain't done yet!
That's it! The perfected
Vacuum Butt Cannon!
It converts rotational
energy into ripples
which hit the enemy!
[MAYA] How'd you do that?
I don't understand how
you could use my deflection
to build up even more energy!
[bellows]
Good job, Maya! Stay strong!
That attack is bound to take
its toll on her eventually!
I know this is tough, but if you
can get through it, you'll win!
[MAYA, NOZOMI yell]
C'mon, push her
off the Land, Nozomin!
--You don't have a lot of time!
--Yeah, hurry!
Hang in there, Maya!
Show 'em how strong Suruga is!
Don't let us down!
[MAYA]
I won't let you defeat me.
I'm determined.
I'll fight to the very end!
--[NOZOMI] Gotcha!
--[MAYA] Oh no, you don't!
What just happened?
[NOZOMI grunting]
I did it! I was worried
I couldn't do it,
but I won, Mom! I beat her!
Now I can repay you
for all you've done for--
[NAGISA] The ripples from
the Vacuum Butt Cannon
cannot be stopped!
Pierce her my nipple!
She used the rotational energy.
Somehow she got it
all the way to her nipples!
[ANNOUNCER 8A] Maya Sakashiro
has gone overboard! Loser!
[bell ringing]
[ANNOUNCER 8A] That bell
marks the end of the race!
And boy, was it a doozy!
For the first time
in its history,
the winners of the eleventh
annual East-West War are...
...Setouchi Keijo
Training School!
[CROWD cheering]
[NON]
Nozomin was amazing, huh?
--[SAYAKA] She won!
--[KAZANE] I'm so happy.
[KAZANE]
I could cry tears of joy!
[ANNOUNCER 8A]
What a fierce battle!
That was one for
the record books, folks!
[ANNOUNCER 8A]
Both teams should be proud
of what they've
accomplished today!
They fought hard!
But, in the end,
Setouchi's perseverance--
no, scratch that--
Nozomi Kaminashi's nipple
changed history!
[ALL]
Hooray!
Oh man, you absolutely
killed it out there today!
I knew that you
could win it for us!
We're super proud
of you, Nozomi!
Oh, here come the tears.
I'm so happy we won--
it's like a dream.
[ATSUKO] Well, guess what?
It's not a dream, we really won.
We did it!
Yeah!
[ALL cheering]
[RIN] All right, ladies!
Let's give it up for our MVP!
[GIRLS] Yeah! Hip hip hooray!
Hip hip hooray!
Hip hip hooray! And in ya go!
[NOZOMI]
Why?
'Cause It's tradition, Nozomin!
[NOZOMI]
I love this sport!
I've raced against
so many awesome players!
[NOZOMI]
Keijo is... friggin' amazin'!
[indistinctive chatter]
[MAYA] Um... I, uh.
I'm really sorry.
I did my best,
but it wasn't good enough.
I'm here because
you saw potential in me.
You took me into your home.
And I repay you by losing.
I let you down. I'm sorry.
If anyone should
apologize, it's me.
You're so much more important
to me than Keijo, Maya.
So you lost a race.
It's no big deal.
I would never punish you
for such a thing.
Thank you, Mom.
[AYAKO]
You made me proud today.
I love you so much.
You're the best daughter
in the world.
I love you, too.
Thank you... for everything.
[MAYA]
After all this time,
I finally feel like
I'm your daughter.
Thanks, Mom.
I'm so glad you
introduced me to Keijo.
[SATOMI]
Kaminashi!
How do you feel
about your win today?
Keijo is... the best ever!
[ANNOUNCER 8A]
After eleven years of losses,
Setouchi is finally taking home
the East-West War trophy!
This year's competition
was intense!
We had some stellar races!
I can't wait to see
what these girls accomplish
when they go pro!
One thing's for sure,
they're going to make a splash
in the Keijo world next season!
[indistinctive chatter]
[NON] Aaah! Goodness,
this is really fancy!
It's just like a ball you'd
read about in a fairy tale.
[SAYAKA]
Everybody was so stressed out
during the East-West War.
I guess this is their way of
letting us blow off some steam.
What's wrong?
What's with that
weird look on your face MVP?
You should be
celebrating right now.
Oh hey, magic girl,
what was your name again?
It's Muromachi.
And I'm Morimoto.
Nice work in the race today.
That was fun.
Thanks, you too.
I gotta admit, I learned
a lot from you both.
Where's Maya?
I dunno, she was still
in her room when I left.
She's been the
top player at Suruga
since she started there.
Today was the first time
she's ever fought someone
who's, like, an equal.
She's prob'ly exhausted.
She fought hard.
And she's been pushing
herself for a while now.
This is the best thing
that's happened to her.
She can sleep soundly
without the weight
of the world on her shoulders.
[HIKARI] You broke through
her defense mechanism.
For all we know, Kaya's gone
and she's finally free
to just be herself.
Really? Well, that's
makes me feel a lot better.
Hey! Raise your hands!
Who here wants to introduce
their friend Hanabi
to a handsome Keijo engineer?
Why're you suddenly
so boy-crazy?
Don't ask me! You do
know players aren't allowed
to date engineers, right?
You don't get it, do you?
Forbidden love is the best kind.
'Cause it's dangerous.
That's why I would
rather spend time
with cute girls than hot guys.
Oh, I see.
Don't get so
worked up now, Usagi.
Trust me, you don't want Midori
sharing your bed with you.
She's cute but she tosses
and turns all night.
[MIDORI]
Shut up, Nami!
[laughing]
[chuckles]
It must be pretty bad, I guess.
Sounds like someone I know.
[NOZOMI]
No way! I don't do that, do I?
[SAYAKA] Just kidding.
Calm down, Nozomi.
[AYAKO] I've been to a lot of
these parties over the years,
but I've never been to one
this lively before.
Apparently, your girls have
taken your "Only Land"
motto to heart.
It's been a while, Ujibe.
Congratulations on your big win.
[NAGISA] Hah. There's no need
to be so formal.
Just call me Nagisa
like you always have.
[AYAKO]
You've got a remarkable team.
Your girls were pulling out
moves and strategies
that I'd never even
thought of using.
That says a lot
about their instructors.
I never would've imagined
you'd train a student
to use the Vacuum Butt Cannon.
[GIRLS gasping, whispering]
[MAYA]
Um. Hello.
Hey are you okay, Maya?
Yes. I feel much better now
that I've taken a little nap.
It's like I'm
full of energy again.
That's great news!
I was really worried,
so hearin' that makes me
full of happiness.
I, uh... I hope I get the
chance to race you uh, someday.
But the next time,
I'm not gonna lose to you!
[chuckles]
We'll see.
[AYAKO] A word of advice,
be sure to prepare them
for what lies ahead.
This is the first time
Setouchi's won
the East-West War.
They'll be targeted
by every pro player,
and that's intimidating.
You're right. But I'm not
worried about my girls.
[ALL]
Cheers!
[NAGISA] They've got
the knowledge and strength
to take on any challenge.
[NOZOMI] This is awesome!
It's hard to believe
I'm registered
as a B-class player!
And I've been assigned
to the Hyogo branch
along with my buddy,
Miyata! Hooray!
Yeah, of course you were.
We're both from Hyogo, silly.
[NOZOMI] I'm glad Oshima and
Rokudou are at the same branch.
But it sucks that everyone else
is goin' their separate ways.
I hate goodbyes. I'm really
gonna miss everybody.
Don't be sad,
we'll see each other again.
It'll just be
on the Land is all!
She's right, y'know!
C'mon, Nozomin! Let's get
everybody together
so we can take some pictures!
And make sure to get
Ms. Ujibe in one, too!
[NOZOMI]
Oh yeah, that's a good idea!
But you might have to shoot in
landscape mode to fit her in.
I don't wanna
be rude or anything,
but she is pretty wide.
[NAGISA]
Hey!
So you're gonna be
disrespectful to your
predecessor right up
till the very end?
Don't forget who taught you!
[NOZOMI chuckles nervously]
I'll never forget!
Ms. Ujibe, thanks for
everything this year.
I'm eternally grateful to you.
And I promise to make you proud!
Thank you.
Don't hurt yourself out there.
But I wanna see you
go wild, got it?
Right!
[KAZANE] You guys're
gonna have to squish
so I can get everyone
in the frame.
Look at Hanabi tryin' to
sneak in next to Nozomin!
We never should've
let them go first
'cause all they're doing
is goofing off.
C'mon, get serious, ladies.
There are other people
waiting to have
their pictures taken!
[KAZANE]
Okay, I've got the timer set!
Everybody say, "Cheese!"
[NOZOMI] I can't wait
till we meet again!
This time
on a professional Land!
Bye-bye!
Thanks again for everything!
[MIKU] I can't believe
how fast this year went by.
Yeah, this place won't
be the same without them.
That's for sure.
You're right.
But they're off to start
a new chapter in their lives.
Our girls are going to
have a major impact
on the professional circuit.
I just hope the Keijo world
is ready for them.
[NOZOMI] Before competing
professionally,
each graduate must undergo a
month-long introductory course.
Their Keijo debut will be
scheduled around Golden Week.
I guess there's
no turning back now.
[NOZOMI]
Hello, ma'am.
We're makin' our
debut this season.
I'm Nozomi Kaminashi
of the Hyogo branch.
Likewise, I'm Sayaka Miyata.
We're thrilled to be here.
We've been waiting for you two.
Hey, ladies!
The kids who started
the Western Japan
revolution have arrived!
[PLAYERS]
We're happy to have you!
Welcome to the pros!
[BOTH]
Thanks!
[ALL]
The rear end!