Announcer:
ALTHOUGH THE COUP D'ETAT
BY A MILITARY FACTION
HAS BEEN DEALT WITH,
TERROR ATTACKS IN THE CAPITAL
ARE STILL CONTINUING.
CITIZENS ARE NOT TO
GO OUTSIDE FOR ANY REASON.
PLEASE REMAIN IN YOUR HOMES.
THIS IS
MARINA ISMAIL,
PRINCESS ROYAL OF
THE KINGDOM OF AZADISTAN.
I URGE EVERYONE LISTENING
TO REMAIN CALM.
WE SHOULD NOT BE
HURTING EACH OTHER,
IN THIS, THE PROMISED LAND
GRANTED TO US BY GOD.
Marina:
THERE IS NO REASON FOR
THIS TO HAPPEN.
IT'S ALL BECAUSE THE REFORMISTS
BROUGHT IN THE UN.
(Patients moaning)
OH,
PRINCESS MARINA,
MAY GOD PROTECT YOU.
WE STILL DON'T HAVE
ANY CLUES
TO MASSOUD RACHMADI'S
WHEREABOUTS?
WORKING TOGETHER WITH
THE UNION,
WE HAVE BEEN
SEARCHING HIGH AND LOW.
BUT WE DON'T ANTICIPATE
FINDING HIM SOON.
I SEE.
(Thinking)
THIS IS THE WORST CASE
SCENARIO.
THE RECEIVER ANTENNAS
HAVE BEEN DESTROYED,
AND THE UN'S ENGINEERS
HAVE WITHDRAWN.
AND NOW WE HAVE CELESTIAL
BEING INTERVENING AS WELL.
THE ONLY WAY OUT OF
THIS SITUATION
IS FOR US TO BRING MASSOUD
RACHMADI UNDER OUR PROTECTION.
IT'S THE ONLY WAY.
♪
Narrator:
THE CIVIL UNREST THAT ERUPTED
IN THE KINGDOM OF AZADISTAN
WAS TRIGGERED BY THE KIDNAPPING
OF RELIGIOUS LEADER
MASSOUD RACHMADI.
WHEN THE TURMOIL ESCALATED
TO THE POINT
WHERE THE MILITARY
LAUNCHED A COUP D'ETAT,
CELESTIAL BEING AND
THEIR GUNDAMS
COMMENCED
AN ARMED INTERVENTION.
WITHOUT THE HELP
OF TACTICAL FORECASTER
SUMERAGI LEE NORIEGA,
WILL SETSUNA F. SEIEI
AND LOCKON STRATOS
BE ABLE TO DEAL
WITH THE SITUATION
AND STOP AZADISTAN'S
INTERNAL CONFLICT?
HMM.
YOU THINK
THERE'S A THIRD PARTY?
YEAH.
ASIDE FROM THE UNION, WHO
WERE CALLED IN TO HELP OUT,
AND US, WHO CAME IN TO
PERFORM AN ARMED INTERVENTION,
THERE'S A THIRD FORCE OUT THERE
THAT WANTS A CIVIL WAR.
AND YOU THINK
THIS THIRD PARTY
IS BEHIND MASSOUD
RACHMADI'S ABDUCTION?
IT'S JUST MY OWN
CONJECTURE, REALLY.
BUT DIDN'T VEDA SAY IT WAS
A POSSIBILITY, AS WELL?
ANY EVIDENCE
OF THIS?
Lockon:
THERE WAS A LONG‐RANGE MISSILE
ATTACK ON THE SITE
WHERE THEY WERE BUILDING
THE RECEIVER ANTENNAS.
FROM THE FIREPOWER,
IT'S LIKELY WE'RE TALKING ABOUT
A MOBILE SUIT HERE.
AN ORGANIZATION WITH ACCESS
TO MOBILE SUITS.
BUT WHY WOULD THEY DO ALL THIS?
LOOK, I DON'T KNOW!
THAT'S WHY I SENT SETSUNA
THERE TO INVESTIGATE.
Lockon:
BECAUSE IN THIS COUNTRY
THE REST OF US
JUST STAND OUT TOO MUCH.
ACCORDING TO
LOCKON'S INFORMATION,
THE MISSILES WERE LAUNCHED FROM
RIGHT AROUND THIS POINT HERE.
RESIDUAL READINGS.
THERE WAS DEFINITELY
A MOBILE SUIT ON THIS SPOT.
BUT WHOSE?
(Gasps)
THE UNION?
Katagiri:
NO DOUBT ABOUT IT,
THESE READINGS CONFIRM
WHAT WE THOUGHT
ABOUT THAT POD WE RETRIEVED.
GUESS THEY'RE INVESTIGATING
THIS AREA, TOO.
WHAT DID THE PMC TRUST
SAY ABOUT IT?
THAT IT WENT MISSING DURING
THE MORALIA CONFLICT‐‐
HUH?
WHAT IS IT?
(Shouting)
IT'S NOT POLITE
TO EAVESDROP!
(Gasps)
(Thinking)
HE SPOTTED ME!
Graham:
SHOW YOURSELF!
(Nervous gasp)
IT'S JUST
SOME LOCAL KID.
I WONDER...
(Nervously)
UM, I...I HEARD THERE'D
BEEN SOME FIGHTING
SOMEWHERE AROUND HERE.
AND I JUST...
NOW I SEE.
IT'S NOT THAT
I DON'T UNDERSTAND
HOW A KID YOUR AGE COULD FIND
THIS STUFF INTERESTING.
BUT THIS PLACE
IS STILL DANGEROUS.
YOU SHOULD GET OUT OF HERE
AS FAST AS YOU CAN.
OKAY. I'LL DO THAT.
EXCUSE ME.
YOUNG MAN!
WHAT DO YOU THINK OF THE
CIVIL UNREST IN THIS COUNTRY?
(Gasps)
UH, GRAHAM?
I SAID, WHAT DO YOU THINK OF
THIS COUNTRY'S CIVIL UNREST?
I... WELL,
I...
Graham:
I BET IT'S HARD FOR YOU
TO BE OBJECTIVE.
ALRIGHT, WHICH SIDE
DO YOU REALLY SUPPORT?
UH, I DON'T SUPPORT EITHER.
BECAUSE I THINK
BOTH SIDES ARE JUSTIFIED.
BUT THEN, MANY PEOPLE
ARE DYING IN THE FIGHTING.
LOTS OF PEOPLE ARE DYING.
I AGREE WITH YOU.
SHOULD A SOLDIER
LIKE YOU SAY THAT?
Graham:
DO YOU CONSIDER US A NUISANCE
FOR COMING TO THIS COUNTRY?
WELL, A LOT OF
SOLDIERS HERE MEANS
THERE'LL BE
A LOT OF CASUALTIES.
Graham:
BUT YOU'RE FIGHTING, TOO.
(Gasps)
WHY DON'T YOU LET ME SEE
WHAT YOU'RE HIDING
BEHIND YOUR BACK THERE?
(Gasps)
(Frustrated grunt)
THAT'S A SCARY FACE.
HMM.
KATAGIRI,
ABOUT THE MOBILE SUIT
THAT ATTACKED THE ANTENNAS
THE DAY
BEFORE YESTERDAY.
WASN'T IT AN ENACT,
THE LATEST AEU MODEL?
Katagiri:
WHY ARE YOU SAYING
THIS RIGHT NOW?
Graham:
AND APPARENTLY,
THAT MACHINE WAS STOLEN
FROM A PMC IN MORALIA.
WE'RE LEAVING NOW.
UH...
(Sighs)
GRAHAM, EXPLAIN TO ME
WHY YOU DID THAT?
YEAH, I WONDER WHY.
MAYBE IT JUST KIND OF
SLIPPED OUT OF ME.
AN ENACT FROM A PMC.
COULD IT BE?!
IT'S HIM.
COULD HE SOMEHOW BE...
INVOLVED IN THIS CIVIL UNREST?
BUT WHY?
I HAVE TO KNOW.
WHY IS HE HERE NOW?
(Screaming)
Daryl:
TERRORISTS AGAIN?!
Howard: IT'S BECAUSE THESE ARE
REFORMISTS NEIGHBORHOODS.
WE CAN'T DEAL WITH THIS
IN MOBILE SUITS.
WE'LL HAVE TO ASK FOR
ANTI‐PERSONNEL
SUPPRESSION AUTOMATONS.
Howard:
THAT AIN'T
GOING TO HAPPEN.
OUR FORCES ARE HERE SPECIFICALLY
TO CAPTURE GUNDAMS.
THE BRASS ISN'T GOING TO DEPLOY
UNNECESSARY MILITARY STRENGTH.
Daryl:
IT'S A TOUGH WORLD,
ISN'T IT?
Woman:
STOP IT!
(Distant gunshots)
Man:
BRING THE WRATH OF GOD!
(Baby crying)
P... PRINCESS MARINA...
Woman:
MAY GOD PROTECT YOU...
WE SHOULD NOT BE HURTING
EACH OTHER, IN THIS‐‐
(Sighs)
I TRY BUT I'M JUST
SO POWERLESS.
(Knock on door)
EXCUSE ME.
WHAT DO YOU WANT HERE?
YOUR DEATH!
PUPPET OF THE REFORMISTS!
(Gunshots)
(Gasps)
(Shocked gasp)
(Heavy sigh)
BUT WHY?
Marina:
WHY?
(Emotional gasp)
I DON'T UNDERSTAND IT!
HOW COULD
WE HATE EACH OTHER ENOUGH
TO RESORT TO SUCH MADNESS?!
HUH?
WHAT IS THAT?
POINT F3987?
WHAT'LL WE FIND THERE?
Setsuna:
MAYBE NOTHING.
BUT THERE USED TO BE
SOMETHING THERE.
WELL, I GUESS IT'S BETTER
THAN DOING NOTHING.
ROGER THAT,
SETSUNA.
MAYBE YOU SHOULD TAKE
HONG LONG WITH YOU.
HUH?
IN CASE OF A RESCUE,
HE COULD BE VERY HELPFUL.
DISENGAGING GN SYSTEM REPOSE.
Setsuna:
PRIORITY PASSED TO
SETSUNA F. SEIEI.
DISSOLVE EXTERNAL
CAMOUFLAGE MEMBRANE,
MAINTAIN GN PARTICLE
DISPERSAL.
ENTER BOARDING MODE.
EXIA, NOW COMMENCING MISSION.
SO MR. HONG LONG,
ARE YOU READY TO GO?
DO WHAT YOU HAVE TO.
ROGER THAT
THEN!
DYNAMES, NOW HEADING TO TARGET!
HERE!
HEY, BOSS.
NOT ONLY IS HE
REFUSING TO EAT,
BUT THE OLD MAN
WON'T EVEN DRINK WATER.
JUST LEAVE HIM ALONE.
HE PROBABLY DOESN'T WANT TO
ACCEPT CHARITY
FROM HIS ENEMIES.
MAN, THE PEOPLE OF THIS COUNTRY
ARE SO DAMN STUBBORN,
AREN'T THEY?
(Gulps)
(Sighs)
THE PLAN IS ALL
MESSED UP NOW BECAUSE OF
CELESTIAL WHATCHAMACALLIT'S
INTERFERENCE.
HEY BOSS!
THERE'S SOMETHING
HEADING OUR WAY!
IS IT A UNION PATROL?
NEGATIVE.
(Grunts)
IT'S THAT WHITE MOBILE SUIT!
(Gasps)
Al‐Saachez:
IT'S A GUNDAM!
EXIA HAS REACHED THE
TARGET POINT.
IF HE'S ANYWHERE, HE'S HERE.
(Beeps)
A MOBILE SUIT!
LET ME DEAL
WITH THE GUNDAM!
TAKE THE OLD MAN AND GET OUT!
Mercenary:
ROGER!
IT'S THAT ENACT AGAIN!
IT'S THAT GUNDAM.
I SEE.
THE PILOT IS
THAT KID FROM KRUGIS!
THEN IT'S NO WONDER
YOU KNOW ABOUT THIS HIDEOUT!
(Metal clashes)
WHAT A SHOCKER!
WHO WOULD'VE GUESSED
THAT LITTLE PUNK
WOULD BE RIDING A GUNDAM!
ISN'T THAT WAR OF YOURS OVER
AND DONE WITH YET?!
HUH?
YOU WANT TO TALK?!
KRUGIS WAS DESTROYED!
(Metal creaking)
(Maniacally)
OF COURSE IT WAS!
WHAT THE HELL ARE YOU
DOING IN THIS COUNTRY?!
TELL ME,
WHERE IS YOUR GOD NOW?!
ANSWER ME!
I DON'T ANSWER
TO YOU!
(Angry grunt)
(Grunts)
(Yelps in pain)
Al‐Saachez:
IT WOULD BE A SHAME TO RUIN
THIS MACHINE.
SO HAND IT OVER TO ME!
HOW ABOUT IT, GUNDAM?!
NOT A CHANCE!
HOW DARE YOU!
HOWEVER,
EVERYTHING'S STILL ON TRACK.
I WOULDN'T BE SO SURE.
HUH?
THAT...
THAT'S A...
A GUNDAM!
HEY, BOSS,
WE'RE UNDER ATTACK!
(Grunts)
DAMN, I'M GETTING
NOTHING HERE!
LOOK THERE!
DAMN IT!
(Grunts)
(Men yell in pain)
YOU BASTARD!
(Painful grunt)
Mercenary:
DON'T MOVE!
Hong‐Long:
I WOULD LIKE YOU TO
HAND THAT MAN OVER.
(Gunshot)
(Two gunshots)
I WAS AFRAID I MIGHT BE
A LITTLE RUSTY BUT I GUESS NOT.
WHO ARE YOU?
WE'RE CELESTIAL BEING.
WHAT IS
"CELESTIAL BEING"?
A PRIVATE ARMED ORGANIZATION
THAT IS INTERVENING
IN YOUR COUNTRY'S
CIVIL WAR.
I SEE.
THAT MEANS YOU'RE ALL...
(Distant whirring)
HUH?
COME ABOARD, PLEASE.
WHAT?
THAT'S IT THEN.
I'VE RECEIVED THE FINAL PHASE,
MISS SUMERAGI.
WHAT KIND OF A MISSION
IS THAT?!
DID YOU REALLY SEND THEM
THOSE INSTRUCTIONS?!
THE SLIGHTEST MISTAKE AND
EXIA COULD BE‐‐
IT'S THE MOST RELIABLE
OPTION OPEN TO US!
SO?!
I AGREE WITH
MISS SUMERAGI'S PLAN.
YOU WHAT?
WE HAVE TO SHOW THE WORLD
WHAT WE REALLY MEAN.
DEMONSTRATE
CELESTIAL BEING'S IDEALS.
Attendant:
PRINCESS MARINA!
WE'VE RECEIVED AN URGENT
MESSAGE FROM CELESTIAL BEING!
FROM CELESTIAL BEING?!
"WE'VE TAKEN MASSOUD RACHMADI
UNDER OUR PROTECTION!"
"WE'RE ON OUR WAY TO THE PALACE.
WE WOULD LIKE THE PRINCESS TO
BEGIN NEGOTIATIONS
FOR AN IMMEDIATE CEASEFIRE."
THAT'S ALL.
I UNDERSTAND.
ARRANGE FOR A CONFERENCE.
IT WILL BE DONE.
PRINCESS MARINA.
I CERTAINLY
DO NOT CONDONE THE ACTIONS
THEY'VE TAKEN
AROUND THE WORLD.
AND THERE IS A CHANCE
THIS IS A TRAP.
BUT, MORE THAN ANYTHING ELSE,
I WANT TO BELIEVE IT.
(Protesters shouting)
Howard:
IS IT TRUE CELESTIAL BEING
IS HEADING FOR THE PALACE?
AND THEY'VE GOT
THE HOSTAGE WITH THEM?
Daryl:
IF IT ACTUALLY HAPPENS THEN
THIS IS OUR CHANCE, LIEUTENANT!
(Grunts)
I'LL BE HERE, GUNDAM,
WATCHING.
(Protesters shouting)
Ikeda:
I'M IN FRONT OF
AZADISTAN'S ROYAL PALACE.
AFTER HEARING THAT
MASSOUD RACHMADI
HAS BEEN TAKEN
INTO PROTECTIVE CUSTODY
AND IS BEING BROUGHT
TO THE PALACE,
THE CITIZENS HAVE BEGUN
GATHERING HERE.
THIS IS STILL UNCONFIRMED
INFORMATION BUT WE'VE HEARD
IT WAS CELESTIAL BEING
THAT ACTUALLY RESCUED RACHMADI.
IS IT POSSIBLE
WE'RE GOING TO SEE
AN APPEARANCE BY
A GUNDAM SOON?
IN ANY CASE, SHOULD A
CONFERENCE
ACTUALLY TAKE PLACE
BETWEEN PRINCESS MARINA ISMAIL,
THE SYMBOLIC HEAD OF
THE REFORMISTS
AND THE CONSERVATIVE RELIGIOUS
LEADER MR. QATAF,
THEN THERE IS NO QUESTION
THAT AZADISTAN WILL BE TAKING
DEFINITE STEPS
TO END THE CIVIL UNREST.
A GUNDAM IS COMING.
(Sighs)
(Irritated grunt)
GET AWAY FROM SAJI!
HE'S MY MAN!
(Protesters shouting)
WHAT'S THAT?!
Howard:
LIEUTENANT!
YEAH, I SEE IT!
PRINCESS!
(Determined grunt)
Ikeda:
IT... IT'S A GUNDAM!
A GUNDAM IS DESCENDING DOWN
ON US FROM ABOVE!
AMAZING!
IT REALLY SHOWED UP!
GUNDAM.
Ikeda:
THE GUNDAM HAS JUST GENTLY
LANDED IN FRONT OF THE PALACE!
IT'S NOT CARRYING ANY WEAPONS!
THE FOOL! SHOWING UP
COMPLETELY UNARMED!
I FORBID YOU TO
ATTACK THE GUNDAM!
Agent:
BUT PRINCESS!
AND THAT IS AN ORDER!
(Distant gunshots)
LEAVE OUR PROMISED LAND NOW!
Ikeda:
THEY'RE SHOOTING!
SEVERAL CITIZENS
ARE FIRING AT THE GUNDAM!
BUT WHY?!
SAJI!
LOOK THERE!
Man:
LET ME GO!
Ikeda:
THE... THE GUNDAM
HAS BEGUN TO MOVE!
IT'S SLOWLY HEADING TOWARD
THE PALACE!
(Panicked shouting)
Pilot:
RELEASE THE HOSTAGE
YOU HAVE IN YOUR POSSESSION!
I REPEAT! RELEASE THE HOSTAGE
Daryl:
LIEUTENANT!
STAND BY, DARYL!
Setsuna:
THIS TIME...
(Surprised gasp)
BUT WHY?!
PRINCESS MARINA!
(Shocked gasp)
GUNDAM.
(People murmuring)
Setsuna:
THIS TIME...
(Thinking)
I'LL BECOME A GUNDAM!
THIS IS THE PALACE.
NOT THE MOST
COMFORTABLE RIDE.
I'M SORRY ABOUT THAT.
YOU HAVE MY THANKS
FOR THIS.
PLEASE HURRY.
Ikeda:
IT'S MASSOUD RACHMADI!
CELESTIAL BEING HAS RESCUED
MR. RACHMADI
AND BROUGHT HIM TO THE PALACE!
(Gasps)
PRINCESS!
IT'S TOO DANGEROUS!
SETSUNA!
IS IT REALLY...
IS IT REALLY YOU UP THERE?
MARINA ISMAIL,
WHAT HAPPENS NEXT
WILL DETERMINE
WHETHER WE COME BACK OR NOT.
SETSUNA.
FIGHT FOR THE GOD
THAT YOU BELIEVE IN.
SETSUNA!
Howard:
LIEUTENANT!
LET'S GO AFTER IT!
Daryl:
WE CAN TAKE IT!
HOW COULD WE?!
TRY SOMETHING LIKE THAT
AND WE'D BE SEEN AS VILLAINS
BY THE ENTIRE WORLD!
(Relieved sigh)
THAT WAS A NERVOUS MOMENT!
I WONDER, YOUNG LADY,
IS THIS REALLY GOING TO SOLVE
THE PROBLEMS THEY HAVE HERE?
NO, PROBABLY NOT.
BUT IT WILL ALLOW PEOPLE
TO TAKE THE FIRST REAL STEPS
TOWARD RESOLVING
THE CONFLICT.
Liu‐Mei:
THEY CAN CERTAINLY DO THAT.
Narrator:
MASSOUD RACHMADI PUBLICLY
ANNOUNCED THAT
A GROUP OF MERCENARIES WAS
RESPONSIBLE FOR THE KIDNAPPING,
AND THAT THE RESULTING
CIVIL UNREST
WAS DELIBERATELY PROVOKED.
IT IS BELIEVED THAT A SHADOWY
ORGANIZATION WAS BEHIND
THIS ATTEMPT TO DERAIL THE
MODERNIZATION OF AZADISTAN.
BUT NO ONE HAS STEPPED FORWARD
TO CLAIM RESPONSIBILITY.
SUBSEQUENTLY, MARINA ISMAIL
AND MASSOUD RACHMADI
RELEASED A JOINT STATEMENT
PLEADING FOR THE CITIZENS
TO END THE CIVIL WAR AND
REFRAIN FROM TERRORISM.
HOWEVER, IN AZADISTAN,
THE CIVIL UNREST CONTINUES.
♪
Narrator:
THE THREE NATIONAL GROUPS
INITIATE A CONFLICT
BY HOLDING
A JOINT MILITARY EXERCISE.
WHAT CROSSES
THE MEISTERS' MINDS
AS THEY HEAD TO THEIR
PLACE OF DEATH?
NEXT EPISODE:
"DAWN OF DETERMINATION".
IS THIS WHAT IT MEANS
TO BE A GUNDAM?