"If the private armed
organization Celestial Being
does not disarm..."
"...and cease its armed
interventions immediately..."
"...our campaign of retaliation
will continue."
"What we do is not evil."
"We are the voice of the people
and apostles in the name of
justice..."
"...rising against those who
oppress the world with military
force."
Man, it had to come to this.
Indiscriminate bombings.
A global terrorist network.
Those bastards!
Lockon! Lockon!
You're angry! You're angry!
Sorry, Haro.
Leave me alone for a little
while.
I'll target them...
Target and fire...
nee konna katachi no deai shika
nakattano? Was this the only way
we could meet?
kanashiine It's so sad
anata ni shindemo ayamete
hoshikumonai... I don't want you
to die or kill anyone...
onegai Please
unmei sae nomikomare We're
sinking into a sea
shizumisouna umi e to A sea that
swallows fate itself
negai yo kaze ni notte May my
wishes ride on the wind
yoake no kane wo naraseyo And
ring the bells of daybreak
tori no you ni May they fly like
birds
My wishes over their airspace
musuu no nami wo koe asu e
tachimukau anata wo You face
tomorrow, crossing myriad waves
mamoritamae Be protected by my
wishes
My life I trade in for your pain
furimukazu habatake Keep beating
my wings without looking back
kono omoi wo hakonde Carrying my
hopes and dreams
ano sora wo tondeku Fly through
the sky
negai wa darenimo uchiotosenai
Wishes can never be shot out of
the sky
Indiscriminate terrorism.
Sure I knew it was a
possibility...
...but this is gonna turn people
against us even more.
It's nothing new, being hated.
Either way, as we're always up
in space, there's nothing we can
do.
We'll leave it to the guys on
the surface.
Welcome home, Mistress.
Please leave us alone for now.
We have business to take care
of.
Excuse us.
Why are you dressed like that?
It's camouflage! Camouflage!
And this is my favorite style!
Do you understand our situation?
I know...
...but right now all we can do
is wait for information from
Wang Liu Mei's agents.
But it sure is hot.
Don't you have any cold beer?
She sure's got a lot of nerve.
She's just acting tough.
If only we could contact those
agents ourselves.
There's no need for us, the
combat team...
...to know everything about the
organization.
I guess I can trust in Veda's
directions...
Long time no see, Feldt! Long
time no see!
Haro.
I've finished contacting all our
agents...
...using an encrypted message on
a special wavelength.
What's the situation in the
various nations?
It appears the intelligence
agencies of the major nations
are already at work...
...searching for the stronghold
of this international terrorist
network.
Another bombing!
It's in the Human Reform League.
With this, the Union, AEU and
Human Reform League...
...have all become targets of
these terrorist attacks.
The probability is high that
it's the work of an
international terrorist network.
We can't deny the possibility
that some country is supporting
it.
It's terrible, having to just
sit and wait like this.
We can surmise...
...that the terrorist network
has several bases of operation.
To make sure we attack them
before they have a chance to
switch bases...
...we'll have all Gundam units
stand by at arranged locations.
Sorry. It's time to say goodbye.
See you, Feldt! See you, Feldt!
Haro.
Disengaging GN System Repause.
Priority to Setsuna F. Seiei.
GN particle dispersal density to
normal levels.
Kyrios, flying to target point.
Virtue, Tieria Erde, launching.
Exia, Dynames, ready to go!
Ready to go!
Exia, Setsuna F. Seiei, heading
to target.
Dynames, Lockon Stratos, taking
off.
A terrorist attack against us
too?
Twenty‐four dead, sixty‐seven
injured.
Intelligence has begun an
investigation.
All right.
Report to me if something turns
up.
Roger that, Lieutenant Colonel!
What's wrong?
I don't believe this is
something...
...you should be involved with,
Lieutenant Colonel.
The reason for these multiple
terrorist acts is Celestial
Being.
Which means there's a
possibility they'll step in at
some point.
Then it's our business.
First Lieutenant, we're not
gonna find the enemy doing this.
I know.
I am a restless, impatient
man...
...and furthermore, I can't
stand those who commit such
cowardly acts.
I know it's nonsense, but I just
can't sit still.
We'll accompany you, First
Lieutenant.
I appreciate your loyalty, guys!
A war in Moralia and multiple
terrorist attacks.
There certainly are a lot of
distractions on your diplomatic
tour, Princess.
Because of the terrorism, my
meeting with the British Foreign
Secretary is postponed.
This is all Celestial Being's
fault.
Think of it as a holiday and
enjoy yourself.
How could you suggest such a
thing to me?
There were complications at the
National Assembly the other day.
The leader of the Conservatives
was attacked and injured by
Reformists.
That's terrible.
It's only a matter of time
before this develops into a
clash between citizens.
This trip may be your first and
last.
Hey, Louise?
It's me. Are you all right?
Terrorist attacks continue
worldwide
I'm fine.
Terrorist attacks continue
worldwide
But Mom's insisting that I
return to Spain.
Go back for a visit and make her
feel better.
No way. She was against me
coming abroad to study to begin
with.
She'll come up with all kinds of
reasons to keep me there.
I'm home.
My sister's home.
See you later, Louise. Let me
know if anything happens.
Sure. See you.
Welcome home. You look
exhausted.
Of course I am.
A large‐scale war in Moralia and
simultaneous terrorist attacks.
Leaders of different nations
making official statements.
Worldwide demonstrations
denouncing Celestial Being.
We can't cover it all, even if
we had every staff member out
there reporting.
Honestly...I used to feel it was
all someone else's problem...
What was?
How do I put it? Everything
that's going on in the world.
Here.
Thanks.
Even after Celestial Being
showed up, there was no conflict
over here.
So I never really thought it
mattered to me.
But then...
...that bus was bombed, and a
lot of people were affected.
When I saw that, I realized it
did matter a lot to me.
I just didn't know it.
I didn't know anything.
That's the same with me.
I just came back from
interviewing the families of the
victims...
...and honestly, it was hard.
They didn't do anything.
They just happened to be
there...
...and their entire lives
disappeared.
I understand why those families
hate Celestial Being.
It's impossible to rid the world
of war.
They're probably thinking the
exact same thing.
What do you mean?
There's something else behind
that impossible goal of
eradicating war.
I bet there's an ulterior motive
that Celestial Being wants to
accomplish.
Though that's just speculation.
But people died. A lot of people
died...
...and there are a lot of people
grieving.
You're right. I totally agree.
I wonder what Dad and Mom would
think if they were alive.
They would be saddened, just as
you are, Saji.
Virtue at target location.
Going into standby.
Kyrios will remain on standby.
How long is this gonna take?
This is so frustrating.
Are you going?
Of course I am.
I'm going to carry out my duty
in the name of God.
No! You'll die!
What? Are you afraid of dying?
That's a blasphemy against God!
He lived for God and died for
God.
Now his spirit will be guided to
There is no God in death.
A heat source detected.
It's close to the predicted
terrorist attack location.
Terrorists, as predicted.
Setsuna here.
We saw a suspicious person
leaving the bombing site on the
security cameras.
You are the closest one to the
scene. Can I have you look into
it?
Roger. I'll head to the site.
You can't use Exia right now.
I know.
Is it true that there was a
terrorist attack?
It is confirmed information.
We've made arrangements for a
hotel in the outskirts of the
city.
The suspect is escaping in a
car. It's a brown coupe.
I will apprehend the target.
Hey! What are you doing?!
What were you trying to do?
Nothing.
Show me your identification!
What's wrong? Hurry and hand
over your identification!
Excuse me. That boy is with us.
Who are you?
This is who we are.
E‐Excuse me!
Mobile Suit Gundam 00
Did I overstep my bounds?
No.
I didn't think I'd meet someone
else from my homeland here.
You're from Azadistan, aren't
you?
No. I'm from Krugis.
Krugis?
I‐I see.
I don't know what to say.
I haven't introduced myself. I'm
Marina Ismail.
Kamal Mazirif.
Are you here on a sight‐seeing
trip?
W‐Wait!
Let me talk to you just a little
longer, please.
We've taken one of the culprits
into custody.
Yes, I will transmit the
biometrics.
Miss, I have confirmed
information.
It has been determined that the
international terrorist
network...
...is the European Nature
Revival Group "La Edenra".
Have our agents locate their
active bases quickly.
Diplomacy?
That's right.
As I'm sure you know, Kamal...
...Azadistan has been split into
the Reformists and
Conservatives.
The country is in chaos.
To rebuild the economy of
Azadistan under the current
restrictions on oil exports...
...we need a solar power
generation system.
But life has become difficult in
our nation...
...because of the solar power
generation system.
So the Conservatives aren't too
pleased with that idea.
Unless we stop the two sides
from confrontation...
...that group will step in.
Celestial Being.
They're a group of fanatics,
thinking they can stop war with
force.
Sure, war isn't right...
...but the reality is that
people are losing their lives...
...in these unilateral
interventions.
Countries have had their
economies ruined.
I wonder, do those people
believe that they're God?
People die in wars, too.
I'm only saying that their
interventions are too arbitrary.
Without any attempt to hold
talks, without looking into
peaceful solutions...
...they're restraining people
with the pressure of violence.
That's not right.
While talks are held, people
die.
Still...!
It was Azadistan that destroyed
Krugis!
You're right.
But right until the end, the two
countries always sought a
peaceful solution...!
And meanwhile, people died!
Kamal, were you...involved?
The fighting ended six years
ago.
But you're still a boy.
Were you fighting?
I am still fighting.
I'm fighting now.
Are you a member of the
Conservatives? Are you here to
kill me?
Killing you won't change
anything.
The world won't change.
Kamal...
No.
My codename is Setsuna F. Seiei.
I'm a Gundam Meister of
Celestial Being!
Celestial Being?
If the conflict doesn't end, we
will eventually go to Azadistan.
‐ N‐No way... ‐ Princess!
That wasn't a very funny joke he
made...
We're getting reports from the
agents now.
La Edenra's main operating bases
have already been abandoned.
They're careful. That brings us
back to square one.
Wait.
The biometric data of a
suspected terrorist has been
released on the network.
A coded message from the NRO?
And the BND and DGSE, too.
Well, Mistress...?
The world is telling us to take
action.
Are you sure it was right to
release that information, Mr.
Secretary?
With our limited jurisdiction...
...we cannot easily take action
against terrorist organizations
in other countries.
However, that group is a little
different.
For this one time, we share
common interests.
La Edenra has three active
bases.
We will attack simultaneously at
1400 Greenwich Mean Time.
Roger.
Virtue will commence attack on
terrorist organization's
operating base.
Kyrios, providing backup.
Enemy strength is unknown.
There's a chance they may have
mobile suits.
Then I'll just shoot them down.
Roger.
Exia, commencing mission.
Disengaging GN System Repause.
Priority to Setsuna F. Seiei.
Dissolve external camouflage
membrane.
Maintain GN particle dispersal.
Enter boarding mode.
Exia, commencing intervention.
All Gundam units have launched.
Miss Sumeragi! Are there any
other orders?
Hm?
No, none at all.
Let's leave the rest up to the
Meisters, and go to the beach!
Are you sure?
You should know that after this
mission we're going back to
space...
I'm going! I'm going! Let's go,
Feldt!
‐ But... ‐ It's okay.
Look out! Over here, Feldt!
Who would've thought so many
nations' intelligence agencies
would help?
That was so nice of them.
We're just being used.
But it's a giant step forward.
It certainly is.
Virtue, target completely
destroyed.
Mission complete.
I'm not holding back.
I'm not giving you any mercy.
Incoming mobile suits!
Sorry, but today...
...don't expect any mercy from
me.
Exia, eliminating targets.
What?!
A mobile armor?
It's old, but I'm surprised they
even have one.
Did that get it?
Exia. Target destroyed.
All Gundam units have destroyed
their targets.
Please advise our agents to
continue monitoring La Edenra's
activities...
...and to look for the country
that supported them.
Very well.
Sometimes, this world is so...
The cradle rocks without knowing
love
Princess, I've been able to
reach Finland's Foreign
Minister...
The cradle rocks without knowing
love
...although I don't think we can
expect much help from them.
As the sleeping forest burns to
ash
My codename is Setsuna F. Seiei.
I'm a Gundam Meister of
Celestial Being!
As the sleeping forest burns to
ash
Impossible.
Even the joy of living together
in peace
Hey, look! A mobile suit!
Even the joy of living together
in peace
Which country is it from?
Even the joy of living together
in peace
That white one, isn't it a
Gundam?
Vanishes into the distance
It's so cool!
Gundam.
Vanishes into the distance
zetsubou wa amai wana Despair is
a sweet trap
tozasareta sono tobira The doors
are locked securely
kokoro ga senjou dakara Because
our hearts are a battlefield
darenimo sukuenai Nobody can
save us
zenmai no shinzou ga unmei ni
ayatsurare Wind‐up hearts are
manipulated by fate
buriki no heitaitachi wa
satsuriku wo hajimeru The hollow
tin soldiers begin the massacre
ai wo shirazu yureru yurikago
The cradle rocks without knowing
love
moetsukiteku nemuri no mori de
As the sleeping forest burns to
ash
tomoni ikiru yorokobi sae mo
Even the joy of living together
in peace
kieteshimau tooku Vanishes into
the distance
yasashisa wo shinji subete wo
yurushite Let us believe in
kindness, and forgive all
itsukushimuyouni Let us treasure
each other
tada wakachiatte wakariatte
Simply sharing and understanding
Celestial Being has gone too
far.
An annihilation operation is
planned with overwhelming
resources.
What is the true objective
hidden within the operation?
Next episode, "The Honor of a
Great Power".
No one can be all‐powerful.