Tribal Chieftain #12A:
RASA! THE ASSEMBLY'S ACTIONS
DEFY THE TEACHINGS OF GOD!
THE LAND OF THIS NATION
WAS GIVEN TO US BY GOD!
HOW DARE THEY BRING INFIDELS
TO THE PROMISED LAND!
THE REFORMISTS WILL STEAL THE
VERY GROUND OUT FROM UNDER US!
RASA...GIVE THE WORD AND LEGIONS
WILL RISE UP AT YOUR CALL!
THE TIME IS NOW!
CALM YOURSELVES. THE PRINCESS
AND THE NATIONAL ASSEMBLY
WILL FACE THE JUDGMENT OF
GOD FOR TURNING
THEIR BACK ON HIS TEACHINGS.
AND SO, WE SHALL WAIT
FOR GOD'S RETRIBUTION.
Tribal Chieftain #12C:
RASA... HOW MUCH LONGER ARE YOU
GOING TO KEEP SAYING THAT?
Tribal Chieftain #12B:
AT THIS RATE, WE'LL END UP
LIKE THE PEOPLE OF KRUGIS!
WE MUST BECOME THE
SWORD OF GOD
AND STRIKE
DOWN THE REFORMISTS!
WE MUST DRIVE THE INFIDELS
OFF OUR LAND!
Tribal Chieftain #12C:
BRING GOD'S LIGHTNING DOWN
UPON THESE CORRUPT REFORMISTS!
Tribal Chieftain #12B:
LET US BE BLESSED!
GOD SHALL SMITE THOSE
WHO FORGET HIS TEACHINGS!
RASA!
RASA! RASA!
(Sighs)
(Gunfire)
WHAT'S THAT?
GUNFIRE!
COULD IT BE
THE REFORMISTS?
RASA!
BANDITS ARE‐‐
(Shot)
(Heavy footsteps)
(Guns loading)
AND WHO ARE YOU?
DO YOU HAVE ANY IDEA
WHERE YOU ARE?
(Chuckles)
♪
Narrator:
THE MIDDLE EAST. MANY OF THE
COUNTRIES IN THIS REGION
HAD BASED
THEIR ENTIRE ECONOMIES
UPON THE EXPORTING OF OIL.
BUT AS A RESULT OF THE SOLAR
POWER GENERATION SYSTEM
CONSTRUCTION PROJECT, THIS
OIL LOST MUCH OF ITS VALUE.
THE UNITED NATIONS RESOLVED
TO PLACE STRICT CONTROLS ON OIL
EXPORTS, WITH FEW EXCEPTIONS.
IN RESPONSE, A NUMBER OF
MIDDLE EASTERN COUNTRIES
TOOK MILITARY ACTION.
THE CONFLICTS MULTIPLIED,
BECOMING THE SOLAR
POWER WARS
THAT WERE WAGED
FOR OVER TWENTY YEARS.
IMPOVERISHED BY THE CONFLICTS
AND ABANDONED
BY THE REST
OF THE WORLD,
MANY COUNTRIES OF THE REGION
HAVE REPEATEDLY DISSOLVED
AND RE‐UNITED IN RESPONSE
TO THEIR ECONOMIC DESTITUTION.
THIS IS THE CURRENT STATE OF
AFFAIRS IN THE MIDDLE EAST.
THE KINGDOM OF AZADISTAN,
LOCATED BETWEEN THE CASPIAN SEA
AND THE PERSIAN GULF,
IS ONE SUCH NATION
THAT IS ATTEMPTING
TO DEAL WITH THIS SITUATION.
TAKING ADVANTAGE OF CIVIL
UNREST WITHIN ITS NEIGHBOR,
SIX YEARS AGO IT ABSORBED
THE REPUBLIC OF KRUGIS.
THE MONARCHY WAS RESTORED
IN THE RESULTING NEW COUNTRY.
DUE TO DIFFERENT
INTERPRETATIONS OF THE
STATE RELIGION, THE POPULATION
HAS SPLIT INTO
TWO RELIGIOUS DENOMINATIONS.
AS A RESULT, THE CURRENT
POLITICAL CLIMATE
REMAINS UNSTABLE.
MASSOUD RACHMADI
HAS BEEN KIDNAPPED
BY AN UNIDENTIFIED
GROUP?
DO YOU KNOW
WHAT THIS MEANS?
THE CONSERVATIVES WILL
LIKELY BELIEVE
THAT WE REFORMISTS
ARE BEHIND ALL THIS.
IN FACT, WE CAN'T RULE OUT THE
POSSIBILITY THAT IT'S TRUE.
IT SEEMS THE UN'S
ASSISTANCE HAS
DONE NOTHING BUT
BRING US MISFORTUNE.
BUT THE ASSEMBLY APPROVED
THE SOLAR POWER GENERATION!
THAT IS TRUE, BUT IT
DOESN'T MEAN
THAT ALL OF OUR
PEOPLE ACCEPT IT.
THE ASSEMBLY HAS
ALREADY DECIDED
TO DEPLOY A
PEACE‐KEEPING FORCE.
IT'S ONLY A MATTER
OF TIME
BEFORE RADICAL
CONSERVATIVES TAKE ACTION.
AND GOD FORBID, BUT
IF BY SOME CHANCE
MASSOUD RACHMADI
SHOULD TURN UP DEAD‐‐
STOP IT!
IT'S JUST TOO AWFUL!
YOU MUST THINK OF
THESE THINGS...
IN ORDER TO
AVOID THE WORST POSSIBILITY.
(Gasps)
THE WORST... POSSIBILITY.
CIVIL WAR.
(Crowd yelling angrily)
LET GOD'S WRATH STRIKE THOSE
WHO'VE FORGOTTEN HIS TEACHINGS!
Hong‐Long:
I CAN'T GET THROUGH
TO PTOLEMAOIS YET.
I EXPECT IT'LL STILL
BE SOME TIME
BEFORE IT'S
BACK FROM LAGRANGE FOUR.
SHOULD CIVIL WAR BREAK
OUT IN AZADISTAN...
WE'LL JUST HAVE TO USE
WHAT WE HAVE AVAILABLE NOW.
(Beeping)
Liu‐Mei:
IT'S ME.
WHAT'S THE SITUATION LIKE?
Alejandro:
THERE SEEM TO BE
SMALL FIGHTS BREAKING OUT
HERE AND THERE,
BUT NOTHING SERIOUS...
YOU SHOULD GET OUT
OF THE COUNTRY.
I'M GOING TO STAY HERE.
STAY THERE? BUT WHY?
I WANT TO SEE WHAT THIS
COUNTRY DOES
AND WHERE
IT GOES NEXT, AND...
I WANT TO SEE FOR MYSELF WHAT
KIND OF ACTION
YOU GUYS WILL
EVENTUALLY DECIDE TO TAKE.
Intern #2A:
I WENT BACK THROUGH THE RECORDS
AND RESEARCHED
THE LAST TWO
HUNDRED YEARS...
THERE ARE AROUND
138 PEOPLE WITH DOCTORATES
WHO'VE EITHER RUN AWAY
OR... GONE MISSING.
CAN YOU RUN A CHECK ON THE
MOST RECENT DISAPPEARANCES?
YEAH, SURE THING.
NEWS FLASH!
MASSOUD RACHMADI, AZADISTAN'S
RELIGIOUS LEADER,
HAS BEEN KIDNAPPED
BY SOME KIND OF ARMED GROUP!
DID HE SAY AZADISTAN?
WE SENT A
REPORTER THERE
TO COVER THE UN'S
TECHNOLOGY AID PACKAGE!
CONTACT HIM
AND GET HIM ON THIS!
RIGHT, BOSS!
SO, DO YOU THINK CELESTIAL BEING
WILL MAKE AN APPEARANCE?
PROBABLY.
OH... MY, THAT LOOKS GOOD!
YOU DIDN'T HAVE TO
GO TO ALL THIS
TROUBLE FOR LITTLE OLD ME!
(Laughs nervously)
I TOLD YOU, MY MOM
LIKES TO GET THINGS!
BUT IT'S ONLY ONE PIZZA.
YOUNG MAN...
YES?
YOUR CLOTHING?
OH...IT'S MY JOB, I WORK
AT THIS PLACE PART‐TIME.
IT'S SO SAD, MOM...
SAJI'S PARENTS PASSED AWAY
WHEN HE WAS LITTLE...
AND NOW HE LIVES ALL
ALONE WITH HIS BIG SISTER.
(Whimpers)
GOODNESS, BOTH PARENTS...
AND NOW YOU'RE FORCED
TO WORK PART‐TIME...
YOU'RE SO BRAVE!
AH...I'M NOT.
MOM CRIES
KIND OF EASILY.
TOO EASILY.
YOU SAID YOUR
NAME'S SAJI, RIGHT?
UH... YEAH.
I CAN SEE NOW THAT YOU
DO HAVE MANLY FEATURES.
D...DO YOU THINK SO?
YOU LOOK LIKE...
LOOK LIKE WHO, MA'AM?
MY DEAR HUSBAND REBORN.
HE DOES NOT AND
DAD IS STILL ALIVE!
RASA...
MASSOUD RACHMADI.
I SEE. SO, YOU'VE MADE
YOUR DECISION THEN.
YES. I'VE DECIDED
TO ACCEPT
AND BECOME THIS
COUNTRY'S PRINCESS ROYAL.
IT DOESN'T MATTER IF
I'M MERELY A FIGUREHEAD,
A SYMBOL OF THE NEW
AZADISTAN,
I FEEL THAT IF THERE'S
SOMETHING I CAN DO TO HELP,
THEN I HAVE TO DO IT.
SO, PLEASE, RASA...
IF YOU DO THEN I SHALL
HAVE NO CHOICE
BUT TO TAKE
THE OPPOSING POSITION.
BUT... WHY WOULD YOU?
PLEASE LISTEN CAREFULLY
PRINCESS MARINA.
THOUGH THIS NATION
OF OURS MAY BE REBORN,
THE PEOPLE LIVING ON ITS LAND
STILL HAVE HISTORY,
THEIR FAMILIES AND
THE HOLY TEACHINGS OF GOD.
MANY OF THEM DISLIKE CHANGE.
AND I DISLIKE IT AS WELL.
IN ORDER TO KEEP
THOSE WHO OPPOSE YOU
FROM RESPONDING WITH VIOLENCE,
THERE MUST BE A FIGURE
WHO CAN TAKE IN THEIR
FEELINGS AND CALM THEIR FEARS.
RASA... HAS EVERYTHING I'VE
DONE UNTIL NOW
JUST BEEN A TERRIBLE MISTAKE?
(Knocking)
SHIRIN. IS THE ASSEMBLY LIKELY
TO LISTEN TO MY OPINIONS?
WILL THE TWO SIDES
AGREE TO COMPROMISE?
THAT IS NOT AN OPTION NOW.
THE CONSERVATIVES ARE
BOYCOTTING THE ASSEMBLY.
AFTER BEING SECRETLY
APPROACHED BY THE UNION,
THE REFORMISTS ARE NOW
DISCUSSING THE IDEA
OF ACCEPTING
MILITARY AID FROM THEM.
BUT DOING THAT WOULD
PROVOKE THE EXTREMISTS
AMONG THE CONSERVATIVES!
AND WHY WOULD THE
UNION GET INVOLVED?
THEY HAVE NO REASON TO
PROTECT THIS COUNTRY.
I'M SURE THEY
HAVE THEIR MOTIVES.
IT'S BEEN A WHILE BUT
WE'LL FINALLY BE FACING
GUNDAMS, LIEUTENANT!
I'D BE DISAPPOINTED
IF WE DIDN'T.
BUT HOW DID WE EVER
END UP IN AZADISTAN?
THE MILITARY BRASS HAVE BEEN
WORKING ON CONGRESS
BEHIND THE SCENES.
WE CAN'T AFFORD TO FALL
BEHIND THE HUMAN REFORM LEAGUE.
PLEASE STAY OUT OF SIGHT
UNTIL THE CIVIL WAR
ACTUALLY ERUPTS.
THEY'RE A LITTLE SMALL
BUT WE DO HAVE ROOMS FOR YOU.
HOW THOUGHTFUL.
HOTEL! HOTEL!
SO WHAT'S THE PLAN?
IN ORDER TO PREVENT THE
IMPENDING CIVIL WAR
WE HAVE TO RESCUE MASSOUD
RACHMADI FROM HIS KIDNAPPERS.
IT'S IMPORTANT WE SHOW HIS
COUNTRYMEN THAT HE'S UNHARMED.
THE PROBLEM IS THE PEOPLE OF
THIS COUNTRY DESPISE OUTSIDERS.
I DON'T KNOW IF WE
CAN PULL THIS ONE OFF.
I'LL SEE
WHAT I CAN DO.
YOU'RE GOING?
WELL, I ORIGINALLY
CAME FROM AZADISTAN.
HMM...
FROM THIS COUNTRY?
HEY SETSUNA...
DON'T GET TOO EMOTIONAL OUT
THERE JUST BECAUSE
IT'S YOUR
HOMELAND THAT'S IN DANGER.
IT'LL BE ALRIGHT.
Liu‐Mei:
VEDA FIGURES THERE'S A HIGH
PROBABILITY THAT THE GROUP
THAT KIDNAPPED MASSOUD
RACHMADI AREN'T REFORMISTS.
Lockon:
YOU MEAN THE CONSERVATIVES
STAGED THIS WHOLE THING?
Hong‐Long:
IT'S ALSO POSSIBLE WE'RE
DEALING WITH A THIRD PARTY.
(Thinking):
THERE ARE PEOPLE WHO
WANT TO START A WAR HERE.
(Footsteps thumping)
(Guns firing)
(Boom)
DO THEY REALLY WANT
IT TO HAPPEN AGAIN?
HUH?
♪
YOU THERE!
WANT TO BUY
SOME WATER?
NO THANKS,
I HAVE ENOUGH.
YOU'RE NOT FROM
AROUND HERE ARE YOU?
YOU'RE RIGHT, I'M KIND
OF A WORLD‐TRAVELER.
(Gasps)
HEY, YOU KNOW, THE CHIEF
TOLD ME THIS GREAT STORY!
HE SAID THERE ARE REALLY
TALL TOWERS IN THE WORLD
AND THEY TAKE YOU INTO
SPACE, IS THAT TRUE?
YEAH...
THEY'RE FOR REAL.
SO HAVE YOU REALLY
BEEN UP THERE?
UH‐HUH.
SWEET!
PRINCESS MARINA SAID
THAT ONE DAY
WE'D BE ABLE
TO GO INTO SPACE, TOO!
MARINA?
YOU DON'T KNOW HER? LOOK...
THERE ARE SOME POSTERS
OF PRINCESS MARINA ISMAIL
RIGHT OVER THERE.
♪
MARINA ISMAIL...
HEY! WHAT ARE
YOU DOING?
I CAN TELL JUST BY YOUR FACE.
FROM KRUGIS, AREN'T YOU?
GRANDPA...
YOU DON'T BELONG AROUND
HERE AND YOU KNOW IT!
GET OUT OF HERE NOW!
HMM?
(Sighs)
WHO WOULD'VE EXPECTED THEY'D
ASK THE UNION FOR ASSISTANCE.
I GUESS THEY DIDN'T KNOW
THERE ARE CONSERVATIVES
IN THE ARMY AS WELL.
SOMEHOW I MUST GET OUT OF
THIS PLACE. AT THIS RATE,
THE COUNTRY WILL ONCE AGAIN
FALL INTO A STATE OF CHAOS.
I WONDER... WHICH SIDE
WILL GOD CHOOSE THIS TIME?
WELL, EITHER WAY,
WE'RE GOING TO HAVE A WAR.
(Chuckles)
(Engine starts up)
Soldier:
WHAT'S THE MATTER?
(Boom)
BRING THE WRATH OF
GOD DOWN
UPON THE INFIDELS
WHO WOULD INVADE OUR LAND!
Daryl:
FIGHTING AT POINT D!
LOOKS LIKE THEY'RE
TARGETING THE ANTENNAS!
LET'S GO!
FLAG FIGHTERS!
Together:
ROGER!
Howard:
LIEUTENANT, THEY'RE FIGHTING
AMONGST THEMSELVES!
WHAT SHOULD WE DO?!
WHICH ONES BELONG
TO THE TRAITORS?
THE RADAR!
(Boom)
WHAT?
THOSE PARTICLE BEAM FLASHES
MEAN... IT'S A GUNDAM!
ALL SHOTS ON TARGET!
STAKING THIS PLACE
OUT WAS A GOOD IDEA.
AND OUT OF NOWHERE!
WHAT THE...
IT'S A MISSILE ATTACK!
THERE ARE JUST TOO
DAMNED MANY OF THEM!
Marina:
THE SOLAR ANTENNAS HAVE
BEEN DESTROYED?
WHO WOULD DO
SUCH A THING?
UNFORTUNATELY, SOME OF THE
MOBILE SUIT PILOTS
THAT WERE ON
SECURITY DUTY WERE EXTREMISTS
WHO SUPPORT THE
CONSERVATIVE CAUSE.
BUT WHY?
Shirin:
ALMOST LIKE
THEY ANTICIPATED
MASSOUD RACHMADI'S
KIDNAPPING...
LIKE SOMEONE IS
BEHIND ALL OF THIS.
THIS WHOLE ATTACK
WAS PLANNED OUT...
BUT BY WHO?
DARYL AND HOWARD!
GO AFTER THE ENEMY
THAT LAUNCHED THE
MISSILES!
I'LL TAKE CARE OF THE GUNDAM!
ROGER THAT!
THE GUNDAM'S ALL YOURS,
CAPTAIN!
HEY, I THOUGHT THE
UNION'S JOB HERE
WAS TO JUST DEFEND AZADISTAN.
SO THEY ARE AFTER US,
AFTER ALL.
TARGET AND FIRE!
(Gasps)
(Straining)
I CALL THAT ONE...
THE GRAHAM SPECIAL!
HARO!
ROGER! ROGER!
IT WON'T HAPPEN TWICE!
MY SHOTS KEEP MISSING!
WHO'S THE PILOT OF THAT THING?
ALLOW ME
TO INTRODUCE MYSELF...
GRAHAM AKER,
AT YOUR SERVICE!
HOW THE HELL WAS HE
ABLE TO KICK ME?
(Growling)
HE ACTUALLY
MADE ME USE MY SWORD!
YOU DON'T LIKE THE PERSONAL
TOUCH, HEY GUNDAM?
Lockon:
HOW ABOUT THIS?
WHAT?
HUH?
Lockon:
HE BLOCKED THEM!
YOU DON'T...
DO THAT TO MY FLAG!
THIS GUY JUST KEEPS
ON COMING!
HARO, CEASE
GN PARTICLE DISPERSAL!
TRANSFER ALL THE
POWER TO THE WEAPONS!
ROGER! ROGER!
Lockon:
ALL THIS
AGAINST A MERE FLAG?
GUNDAM...
(Voice on radio):
MOBILE SUITS HAVE BEEN
SPOTTED LEAVING
THE AZADISTAN
ARMY'S ZAYER BASE.
THEY'RE HEADING FOR
THE PALACE.
AN EMERGENCY CALL...
ALL UNITS ARE TO HEAD
THERE AND INTERCEPT THEM.
Liu‐Mei:
I EXPECT WE'LL BE
SEEING SOME MOVEMENT
AT THE OTHER BASES
AS WELL.
THE AZADISTAN ARMY...
MOBILE SUITS LEFT THE ZAYER
BASE WITHOUT ANY ORDERS?
THIS MEANS... A COUP D'ETAT!
THERE ARE FIVE
MOBILE SUITS IN TOTAL
AND ALL OF THEM ARE HEADING
STRAIGHT FOR US.
Attendant:
PRINCESS!
EVACUATE TO THE SHELTER!
Marina:
BUT I...
PLEASE, HURRY!
(Voice on PA):
WE ARE THE SWORD OF GOD!
WE WILL RISE UP AGAINST THEM!
BRING THE WRATH
OF GOD DOWN UPON THOSE
WHO HAVE FORGOTTEN
HIS TEACHINGS!
CHASE OUT THE
INFIDELS WHO HAVE TRESPASSED
UPON OUR PROMISED LAND!
(Rocket fires)
SHOULDN'T WE BE
EVACUATING?
AH, RIBBONS...YOU SHOULD
TAKE A LOOK AT THIS AS WELL.
A GUNDAM WILL BE
COMING VERY SOON.
(Engine roaring)
SETSUNA F. SEIEI...
EXIA, WILL ELIMINATE
THE TARGETS!
SOUNDS LIKE A COUP D'ETAT.
SO WHAT'LL YOU DO...
MR. FLAG PILOT?
AFTER FINALLY
MEETING A GUNDAM!
DISAPPOINTING TO
SAY THE LEAST...
BUT A MAN
HAS HIS OBLIGATIONS!
HOWARD! DARYL!
HEAD FOR THE CAPITAL!
Together:
ROGER!
ANYTHING ON WHO
FIRED THE MISSILES?
Daryl:
WE SAW THE SILHOUETTE OF A
MOBILE SUIT
BUT BECAUSE OF
THOSE SPECIAL PARTICLES...
SOMETIMES GUNDAM ABILITIES
HAVE DRAWBACKS.
(Slashing)
Ribbons:
SO THAT IS A GUNDAM.
THAT WAS JUST
BRUTE FORCE.
HE'S RELYING TOO MUCH ON
THE GUNDAM'S ABILITIES.
THE PILOT IS
SETSUNA F. SEIEI.
(Beeping)
HUH?
WHAT IS IT?
THE KAZUNA BASE HAS
DEPLOYED A MOBILE SUIT TEAM.
THEY'RE PASSING THROUGH
THE KEHI REGION RIGHT NOW.
ROGER.
Lockon:
GIVE ME A BREAK! IT'S ONE
THING AFTER ANOTHER!
HUH?
WHAT IS THIS?
(Gasps)
(Stomping)
(Guns firing)
(Boys panting)
(Boom)
(Exhales heavily)
(Guns firing)
(Coughing)
(Firing)
(Children firing)
♪
EXIA!
(Sparking)
♪
(Gasps)
(Firing)
(Bullets ricocheting)
(Roars)
CELESTIAL BEING HAS BEGUN
AN ARMED INTERVENTION
IN THE
KINGDOM OF AZADISTAN,
A MIDDLE EASTERN
NATION RECEIVING
UN TECHNOLOGICAL
ASSISTANCE.
SO WHERE IS THIS
AZADISTAN PLACE?
UH...IN THE MIDDLE
EAST I THINK...
STOP SITTING SO CLOSE!
Reporter:
HOWEVER, WHY THIS UNREST
AT A TIME WHEN ENERGY IS
ABOUT TO BE SUPPLIED TO THEM
WITH THE SUPPORT OF THE UN?
Christina:
MISS SUMERAGI!
WE'RE RECEIVING AN URGENT
CODED MESSAGE FROM VEDA!
(Gasps)
Sumeragi:
A COUP D'ETAT
IN AZADISTAN?
(Planes flying)
OUR REINFORCEMENTS HAVE TAKEN
CONTROL OF THE AIRSPACE
THROUGHOUT THE CAPITAL REGION.
WHEN RELIGIOUS DEVOTION GETS
OUT OF CONTROL,
THIS KIND OF TRAGEDY
IS THE INEVITABLE RESULT.
DAMN YOU...
WELL, YOU STOPPED IT,
GUNDAM...
TOO BAD, THE
FUN WAS JUST BEGINNING!
WE SUFFERED A COUP D'ETAT...
AND THEN THERE
WAS AN INTERVENTION
IN OUR COUNTRY BY
CELESTIAL BEING.
WE'RE UNDER THE PROTECTION OF
THE UNION MILITARY NOW.
THE COUP D'ETAT IS
FADING FAST...
PLEASE BE
AT EASE, PRINCESS.
BUT NOW THE HEARTS
OF THE PEOPLE
HAVE BEEN LIT WITH
THE SEARING FLAMES OF ANGER.
EVERYTHING I'VE DONE SO FAR
HAS ONLY LED THIS COUNTRY
INTO BITTER CONFLICT.
(Weeping)
Shirin:
MARINA ISMAIL...
BE RESOLUTE!
(Gasps)
IT IS NOT OVER YET!
NOT YET...
THIS IS TERRIBLE...
EXIA FOUND!
SETSUNA...
♪
I CANNOT...
BECOME A GUNDAM.
♪
Narrator:
ALI AL‐SAACHEZ STANDS
BEFORE SETSUNA,
WHO HAS HAD HIS
CONVICTIONS SHATTERED.
EXIA RISES AGAIN TO
ELIMINATE CONFLICT.
NEXT EPISODE:
"RETURN OF THE SAINT".
SETSUNA BECOMES A GUNDAM.