Howard:
LIEUTENANT... IS IT TRUE
THE HUMAN REFORM LEAGUE
FOUGHT A BATTLE WITH THE
GUNDAMS IN SPACE?
YEAH.
AND I HEARD THAT, JUDGING FROM
THE DEBRIS ALONE,
OVER TWENTY TIERENS
WERE SERIOUSLY DAMAGED.
(Whistles)
NO WAY. KIND
OF SCARY JUST THINKING ABOUT
GOING UP
AGAINST THOSE THINGS.
YEAH, NO KIDDING.
YEAH, WELL MOBILE SUIT
PERFORMANCE ISN'T THE ONLY THING
THAT DETERMINES WHO'S GOING
TO WIN A FIGHT.
I KNOW YOU'LL
DO ME PROUD...
FLAG FIGHTERS.
SO, THOSE SPECIAL
PARTICLES
ARE ACTUALLY
DIVERSELY MUTABLE PHOTONS.
YES, BUT THAT'S NOT ALL.
THE GUNDAMS SEEM
TO BE PRODUCING THESE
UNIQUE PARTICLES WITHIN
THEIR ENGINES.
I DON'T KNOW HOW
ELSE TO EXPLAIN
THEIR SEEMINGLY
LIMITLESS FLIGHT RANGE
AND EXTENDED
OPERATION TIME.
THAT MUST HAVE SOMETHING
TO DO WITH THE FACT THAT
ONLY FOUR GUNDAMS HAVE
MADE AN APPEARANCE SO FAR.
AEOLIA SCHENBERG WAS A
MAN OF SUPERHUMAN GENIUS.
TO THINK HE DISCOVERED THIS
PARTICLE AND ESTABLISHED
ITS BASIC THEORY
OVER TWO CENTURIES AGO.
HMM...
WHY WOULD A MAN LIKE THAT
INITIATE SUCH AN UNREALISTIC
PROJECT AS THE ELIMINATION
OF WAR FROM THE WORLD?
TO WARN HUMANITY WHO
SEEM ON THE VERGE
OF BRINGING THE SEEDS
OF WAR UP INTO SPACE.
AT LEAST, THAT'S
HOW I SEE IT.
♪
Tieria:
IN THE MILITARY OPERATION
THAT WAS CARRIED OUT
BY THE HUMAN REFORM LEAGUE,
KYRIOS WAS NEARLY CAPTURED
AND NADLEEH WAS
REVEALED TO THE ENEMY.
SUMERAGI LEE NORIEGA,
AS COMMANDER
OF THE OPERATION,
EVERYTHING THAT HAS HAPPENED
IS YOUR FAULT.
I AM SORRY. BUT AS YOU KNOW,
I'M ONLY HUMAN,
THERE ARE TIMES
WHEN I DO MAKE MISTAKES.
THAT'S NO EXCUSE FOR WHAT
OCCURRED HERE.
DO YOU KNOW HOW MUCH THIS
WILL SET THE PLAN BACK?
YOU'RE THE ONE
WHO PANICKED
AND SHOWED
NADLEEH TO THE ENEMY.
IF I HADN'T, THEY'D
HAVE CAPTURED ME.
THAT MAY BE SO,
BUT YOU'RE STILL
PARTIALLY
RESPONSIBLE FOR IT.
YOU CAN'T BLAME ALL OF THIS
ON MISS SUMERAGI.
COUNT YOUR BLESSINGS
THAT YOU'RE STILL ALIVE.
I'LL BE GIVING VEDA'S COMMANDS
TOP PRIORITY FROM NOW ON.
EXCUSE ME.
(Sighs)
WELL, THAT WAS
SURE TENSE.
HE DIDN'T HAVE TO COME
IN HERE WITH
AN ATTITUDE AND SAY IT IN
FRONT OF EVERYONE LIKE THAT.
I THINK IT'S CUTE HOW UPTIGHT
THE GUY IS...
HE'S ANGRY WITH HIMSELF
SO HE TAKES IT OUT ON OTHERS.
(Thinking):
THAT MACHINE...
A HIGH‐MOBILITY
SUPER‐SOLDIER
VERSION OF THE TIEREN.
THERE'S NO DOUBT ABOUT IT.
THAT PILOT IS JUST LIKE ME.
THEY'RE NOT STILL WORKING ON
THAT PROJECT...ARE THEY?
THAT ACCURSED PROJECT.
Commander #4A:
THE DATA COLLECTED ON THE
WINGED GUNDAM
DURING ITS CAPTURE,
IMAGES FROM THE
TIERENS' MISSION RECORDERS
OF THE CELESTIAL BEING'S
MOTHER SHIP
AND THE BIG
ONE SHEDDING ITS ARMOR.
IT'S SIMPLY NOT WORTH THE
COST OF SEVERAL HUNDRED
THOUSAND PROBES AND
MORE THAN TWENTY TIERENS.
I HAVE NO EXCUSE, SIR.
I AM PREPARED TO FACE
DISCIPLINARY ACTION.
I HAVE NO PLANS TO RELIEVE YOU.
AND YOU CAN NOT RESIGN.
HMM?
IT'S TRUE THE OPERATION
WAS A FAILURE...
BUT THAT HASN'T CHANGED MY
EVALUATION OF YOU ONE BIT.
THE GUNDAMS' ABILITIES
SIMPLY SURPASSED
ALL OF OUR
EXPECTATIONS.
EXCUSE ME, SIR,
BUT WE STILL DON'T KNOW
WHAT THEIR TRUE LIMITS ARE.
CONTINUING THIS CAPTURE
OPERATION COULD BE VERY COSTLY‐‐
I'M AWARE OF THAT AS WELL.
THE CHAIRMAN IS
CURRENTLY CONDUCTING SECRET
NEGOTIATIONS WITH THE UNION.
TALKS WITH THE UNION?
THIS MEANS THAT THE
CELESTIAL BEING SITUATION
IS MOVING TO THE NEXT
PHASE OF ENGAGEMENT.
Ivan:
LIEUTENANT PERIES...
PLEASE,
AVENGE LIEUTENANT MING
IN THE NEXT OPERATION...
NO... AVENGE ALL
OUR COMRADES!
I WILL COMPLETE MY MISSIONS
THE BEST THAT I CAN.
BECAUSE THAT IS
ESSENTIALLY
THE ONLY REASON THAT
I AM PERMITTED TO EXIST.
(Allelujah on recording):
STAY BACK!
(Screams)
AS THE LIEUTENANT'S TAOZI
APPROACHES,
THE GUNDAM PILOT
EXPERIENCES INCREASED PAIN.
CLEARLY, THE PILOT IS
BEING AFFECTED
BY THE QUANTUM BRAIN WAVES.
(Computer beeps)
THERE IS ONE.
TEST SUBJECT E‐57.
E‐57. AFTER QUANTUM
BRAIN WAVE TREATMENT.
NEW PERSONALITY MANIFESTED
FEROCIOUS TENDENCIES...
AFTER DATA
WAS COLLECTED... DISPOSED OF.
THIS ISN'T GOOD.
IF THE TOP BRASS FINDS
OUT ABOUT THIS THERE'S‐‐
(Gasps)
DID YOU FIND OUT ANYTHING
FROM EXAMINING THE
TAOZI'S MISSION RECORDER?
WELL...
NOTHING SIGNIFICANT YET, SIR.
I BELIEVE THE
GUNDAM PILOT
AND LIEUTENANT
PERIES ARE THE SAME TYPE.
I CAN'T RULE OUT THE POSSIBILITY
THAT OTHER COUNTRIES
MIGHT BE RESEARCHING QUANTUM
BRAIN WAVE TREATMENT AS WELL.
IF THEY ARE,
THEN IT JUST SHOWS
HOW TWISTED THIS WORLD
REALLY IS.
I'M AFRAID I HAVE TO AGREE WITH
YOU ON THAT POINT, COLONEL.
WHAT SHOULD I DO?
SHOULD I REPORT THIS?
OR SHOULD I JUST‐‐
THERE'S ONLY ONE
THING YOU CAN DO!
HALLELUJAH.
THAT DETESTABLE LABORATORY IS
STILL IN EXISTENCE
AND IT'S
STILL CHURNING OUT PEOPLE
LIKE YOU AND ME ONE AFTER
THE OTHER...
WHICH MAKES THAT INSTITUTE
GUILTY OF PROMOTING WAR.
YOU WANT ME TO DESTROY IT?
AND THE PEOPLE LIKE US.
IS THE KIND‐HEARTED
MR. ALLELUJAH
TOO GOOD
FOR THAT KIND OF WORK?
THEN HAND YOUR BODY
OVER TO ME,
I'LL DEAL WITH
THE ISSUE REAL QUICK.
JUST LIKE I DID BEFORE.
(Child's voice)
ARE WE GOING TO DIE?
OH, NO! I DON'T WANT TO DIE!
ALLELUJAH! ALLELUJAH!
IT'S NO GOOD!
YOU'RE GOING TO DIE!
ALLELUJAH, PLEASE‐‐
NO... MY NAME IS‐‐
(Gasps)
NO, FORGET IT,
HALLELUJAH.
WE DON'T HAVE TO
KILL ANYONE!
WE COULD JUST
TAKE THEM INTO CUSTODY!
WHAT FUTURE DOES
A PERSON WHO WAS REBUILT
FOR COMBAT POSSIBLY HAVE?
YOU KNOW THE ANSWER TO THAT
BETTER THAN ANYONE.
YEAH, CELESTIAL BEING'S
MR. GUNDAM MEISTER.
YOU'RE WRONG! THE REAL
REASON I CAME HERE WAS‐‐
BECAUSE THE ONLY THING
YOU CAN DO IS FIGHT!
NO!
BECAUSE THAT IS OUR DESTINY!
YOU'RE WRONG!
I'M NOT...
(Gasps)
SETSUNA...
SOMETHING WRONG?
UH, NO...NOTHING'S WRONG.
Alejandro:
I UNDERSTAND THE CONSTRUCTION
OF THE RECEIVER ANTENNAS
HAS FALLEN BEHIND SCHEDULE.
Marina:
THE CONSTRUCTION HAS BEEN
INTERRUPTED A NUMBER OF TIMES.
THERE ARE SOME ELEMENTS
AMONG MY PEOPLE
WHO ARE OPPOSED TO
SOLAR POWER GENERATION.
PLEASE, WE'D LIKE YOU
TO MAKE THE SAFETY
OF OUR ENGINEERS
YOUR TOP PRIORITY.
IF SOMETHING HAPPENED WE'D
REALLY HAVE NO CHOICE
BUT TO LEAVE
YOUR COUNTRY.
I UNDERSTAND AND I'VE CONVEYED
YOUR CONCERNS TO THE ARMY.
YOUR HIGHNESS...
WHY NOT TAKE SOME TIME
TO PAY A COURTESY VISIT
TO THE CONSTRUCTION SITE?
IT WOULD GREATLY
IMPROVE THE MORALE
OF THE SOLDIERS AND
ENGINEERS‐‐
SO THAT SHE CAN
BE ASSASSINATED?
Marina:
SHIRIN!
AMBASSADOR CORNER,
WHY DID THE UNITED NATIONS
DECIDE TO GRANT TECHNICAL
ASSISTANCE TO AZADISTAN?
IN THE MIDDLE EAST
THERE ARE MANY COUNTRIES
THAT
ARE TECHNOLOGICALLY BACKWARDS.
SO WHY WOULD YOU HELP US?
THE SIMPLEST ANSWER IS THAT
YOU REQUESTED OUR ASSISTANCE.
THE UNITED NATIONS WISHES TO
EXTEND ITS SUPPORT
TO ALL THE
LANDS OF THE MIDDLE EAST,
AND WE WOULD LIKE TO
MAKE A MODEL CASE
OUT OF THE
KINGDOM OF AZADISTAN.
AND THE EXISTENCE OF CELESTIAL
BEING IS A CONCERN AS WELL.
CELESTIAL BEING...
THEY SEEK THE ERADICATION
OF WAR
AND SINCE THE MIDDLE
EAST IS PLAGUED BY PERPETUAL,
ALBEIT SMALL, CONFLICTS, THEIR
INTERVENTION IS INEVITABLE.
RATHER THAN SENDING
ASSISTANCE TO REBUILD,
I BELIEVE IT IS FAR
MORE BENEFICIAL
TO HELP ALLEVIATE THE
CONFLICTS IN THE FIRST PLACE.
THAT'S A NOBLE
SENTIMENT, INDEED.
AMBASSADOR...
CAN YOU SWEAR BY YOUR GOD
THAT THOSE FEELINGS
AND SENTIMENTS ARE TRUE?
ABSOLUTELY. AND
BY YOUR GOD AS WELL...
FOR AZADISTAN'S FUTURE.
(Ice clinks)
WHAT IS IT, ALLELUJAH?
LET ME GUESS, YOU'RE
ANGRY WITH ME TOO?
YOU'VE BEEN
THROUGH A LOT,
SO I WOULDN'T BLAME
YOU ONE BIT.
I'M SORRY FOR BEING SUCH
A LOUSY TACTICAL FORECASTER.
UH, ARE YOU DRUNK?
IS THAT A PROBLEM?
MAYBE YOU SHOULD
THINK ABOUT TAKING IT EASY.
NO WAY. THIS IS THE
ONLY THING
THAT MAKES ME
WANT TO KEEP ON LIVING.
LISTEN...IF YOU DON'T
HAVE ANYTHING‐‐
I HAVE A PROPOSAL FOR
A MISSION PLAN
I WANT TO
RUN BY YOU AND VEDA.
A MISSION PLAN?
YES, IT'S AN
ARMED INTERVENTION MISSION
AGAINST AN INSTITUTE
THAT PROMOTES WAR.
THIS INSTITUTE IS A VERY
IMPORTANT PLACE FROM MY PAST.
I'VE COLLECTED DETAILED
DATA ON IT.
PLEASE TAKE A LOOK
AT IT WHEN YOU'RE SOBER.
EXCUSE ME.
(Door slides open)
(Door closes)
HUH?
HUMAN REFORM LEAGUE,
SUPER SOLDIER SPECIAL DUTY
IT IS TRUE!
I'M GOING TO END THIS
NIGHTMARE ONCE AND FOR ALL!
AND THIS TIME...
IT'LL BE MY WILL!
Louise's mother:
OOH!
MY GOODNESS, LOUISE!
THE FACT YOU CAN
PREPARE JAPANESE
FOOD SO PERFECTLY AMAZES ME!
COME ON, TRY SOME! I SWEAR
IT'S REALLY, REALLY GOOD!
MMM...
OH!
IT'S GOOD, HUH?
YES, IT'S VERY GOOD.
HEY MOM SAYS THE MEAL
IS VERY GOOD... SAJI!
WHAT?
UH...THANK YOU.
WELL, JUST BECAUSE YOU CAN
COOK DOESN'T MEAN I APPROVE OF
YOU HAVING A RELATIONSHIP
WITH MY DAUGHTER.
I MUST ADMIT, THOUGH
THAT I DO APPROVE
OF YOUR COOKING.
WELL, I'M JUST GLAD
YOU LIKE IT, MA'AM.
DEAD END.
MISS KINUE,
DO YOU HAVE ANY IDEA
HOW WE CAN TRACE THE
MOVEMENTS OF AEOLIA SCHENBERG?
ALL OF HIS RELATIVES ARE DEAD
AND EVEN IF YOU TRIED
TO TRACK HIS FINANCES,
DATA SECURITY WAS FULL OF HOLES
TWO HUNDRED YEARS AGO.
I MEAN, IT COULD'VE BEEN ALTERED
BY NOW. IT'S NOT POSSIBLE.
I KNOW, THAT'S
WHY WE'RE SITTING HERE...
WHAT DO YOU MEAN?
IT'S THEM!
WHO ARE THEY?
THEY'RE FROM THE UNION'S
SECURITY BUREAU.
HUH? FROM THE
UNION SECURITY BUREAU?
THEY'RE ALSO AFTER AEOLIA AND
I RECEIVED SOME INFORMATION
THAT THEY'VE BEEN HERE
THREE TIMES ALREADY THIS MONTH.
THIS IS PRETTY RISKY STUFF,
MISS KINUE!
LOOK, IF THEY FIND
OUT WHAT WE'RE UP TO...
WAIT! WAIT A MINUTE...
MISS KINUE!
I LOOKED AT EVERYTHING...
THE MISSION PLAN,
AS WELL AS YOUR PAST HISTORY.
WE DO HAVE GROUNDS FOR AN
ARMED INTERVENTION AND VEDA
HAS RECOMMENDED THE
OPERATION AS WELL.
BUT ARE YOU SURE GOING AFTER
PEOPLE WHO ARE LIKE YOU...
NO PROBLEM.
WHAT DOES
THE OTHER YOU SAY?
THERE'S NO NEED
TO ASK HIM.
ARE YOU SURE ABOUT THAT?
I'LL FACE MY OWN PAST...
AND I WILL DO IT ALONE.
VERY WELL, THEN.
EXIA, DYNAMES...YOU'LL CARRY OUT
AN ARMED INTERVENTION
IN THE
CONFLICT ZONE
ALONG THE SOUTH AFRICAN
BORDER AS PLANNED.
AFTER THE TWO MACHINES
HAVE LAUNCHED,
THE PTOLEMY WILL
SET COURSE FOR LAGRANGE FOUR.
WE'LL BE MOVING AGAINST A HUMAN
REFORM LEAGUE INSTITUTE
SITUATED AT THE
QUANQUI SPACE COLONY.
(Machines humming)
Feldt:
LAUNCH PREPARATIONS COMPLETE.
TRANSFERRING TIMING
CONTROL OVER TO EXIA.
DON'T DO ANYTHING CRAZY
JUST BECAUSE I'M NOT THERE.
ROGER THAT.
EXIA, SETSUNA F. SEIEI...
HEADING OUT.
(Whoosh)
Feldt:
NEXT... PREPARING FOR
DYNAMES' LAUNCH SEQUENCE.
COMMENCING CONTAINER LOADING.
DYNAMES TO THE CATAPULT DECK.
I'VE LOOKED AT
THE MISSION PLAN
AS WELL AS YOUR
PAST HISTORY.
BUT ARE YOU SURE GOING AFTER
PEOPLE WHO ARE LIKE YOU...
NO PROBLEM.
ALLELUJAH HAPTISM.
I SEE.
HE IS...
HUMANITY... HOW COULD PEOPLE
EVER DO ANYTHING SO FOOLISH?
THEY JUST WANTED TO KNOW WHERE
YOUR GREAT‐GRANDFATHER WENT?
YES. I WAS TOLD
NOT TO TELL ANYONE.
THE SECURITY BUREAU HAS
BEEN GATHERING INFORMATION
ON MY GREAT‐GRANDFATHER,
WHO WENT MISSING
A LITTLE OVER
TWO HUNDRED YEARS AGO.
CAN YOU TELL ME WHAT KIND
OF PERSON HE WAS?
THEY TELL ME HE WAS AN AUTHORITY
IN MATERIALS ENGINEERING
BUT I DON'T
KNOW THE DETAILS.
SO IN THE END WE
STILL HAVE NO CLUES.
NOT NECESSARILY. IT SEEMS
LIKE AEOLIA SCHENBERG
WAS PROBABLY SCOUTING
AND RECRUITING SCIENTISTS
HE COULD USE FOR HIS PROJECT
EVEN BACK THEN.
GRANTED YOU
CAN HACK INTO DATA
BUT YOU CAN'T DO
THAT WITH PEOPLE.
IT'S STARTING
TO COME INTO FOCUS...
THE SHADOW OF A MAN WHO
DIED TWO CENTURIES AGO.
(Boom)
AN EASY WIN DOWN HERE,
BUT I WONDER HOW
THE OTHER TWO ARE DOING.
Feldt:
KYRIOS, VIRTUE...
LAUNCHES COMPLETE.
0042 UNTIL MISSION START TIME.
Lasse:
HUH, SO THAT'S THE HUMAN
REFORM LEAGUE'S SPACE COLONY.
I HONESTLY NEVER THOUGHT I'D
SET EYES ON THIS PLACE AGAIN...
I'LL TAKE CARE OF
THESE GUYS, LIKE WE PLANNED.
YOU TAKE OUT THE TARGET.
I APPRECIATE THAT.
IF THAT MAN IS BEING CORRUPTED
BY THE THING HE
CALLS A PAST
THEN HE NEEDS TO PURIFY
HIMSELF WITH HIS OWN HANDS.
THAT'S WHAT IT MEANS TO
BE A GUNDAM MEISTER!
(Guns blasting)
(Boom)
♪
(Laser beam hums)
(Computer beeps)
SECURITY INFILTRATION
COMPLETE.
FROM HERE ON IN...
I'LL JUST WING IT!
HUH?
WHAT?
A GUNDAM!
IT'S CELESTIAL BEING!
WHERE ARE THE
DEFENSE FORCES?
THEY'RE FIGHTING ANOTHER
GUNDAM OUTSIDE!
SEAL THE HATCH
IMMEDIATELY!
IT'S NO GOOD, SIR!
THE DATA'S BEEN OVERWRITTEN!
THE GUNDAM'S
ENTERING THE COLONY!
HUH? I'M CAUGHT UP
IN THE AIR CURRENTS!
SYNCHRONIZING KYRIOS
TO COLONY ROTATION.
CELESTIAL BEING IS HERE?!
DON'T THEY KNOW
THERE'S A TREATY
PROHIBITING ANY
COMBAT INSIDE COLONIES?!
TERRORISTS DON'T CARE
ABOUT THINGS LIKE THAT!
BUT WHAT'S THEIR OBJECTIVE?
JUST AS MISS SUMERAGI
FORECASTED...
THEY WON'T
FIGHT INSIDE THE COLONY.
(Gasps)
(Young voices screaming)
THEY'RE HERE...
THE ONES LIKE ME...
IN THAT ACCURSED PLACE!
LET'S GO!
I WON'T HESITATE
BECAUSE I'M A GUNDAM MEISTER!
(Children screaming):
STOP IT!
IT HURTS!
MY HEAD...
OWW! OWW!
IS IT NECESSARY TO
KILL THEM?
I MEAN I COULD TAKE
THEM INTO CUSTODY...
YOU'RE SO WEAK...
HALLELUJAH?
TAKE THEM INTO CUSTODY,
HOW? HOW WILL YOU RAISE THEM?
HAVE YOU BEEN ABLE TO
LIVE A NORMAL LIFE
AFTER ESCAPING THIS PLACE?
(Chuckles)
STOP THINKING ABOUT
THINGS YOU CAN'T CHANGE!
I KNOW BUT...THEY'LL HAVE LIVES
OF MISERY IF I JUST LEAVE THEM!
MISERY?
MISERY, YOU SAY...
THOSE KIDS IN THE LAB
DON'T THINK OF THEMSELVES
AS MISERABLE.
BUT THEY'LL FEEL
THAT WAY EVENTUALLY!
WELL, DO YOU THINK THAT
GIRL FLYING THE TIEREN
FEELS SHE HAS
A MISERABLE LIFE?
THAT'S NOT THE CASE, IS IT?
DON'T PUSH YOUR OWN FEELINGS
ONTO OTHERS.
NO MATTER WHAT
PRETTY WORDS YOU STRING
TOGETHER, YOUR KINDNESS
IS JUST HYPOCRISY.
YOU'RE PRETENDING TO BE NICE
JUST TO MAKE YOURSELF
FEEL BETTER.
BUT THEY'RE ALIVE!
THEY'RE NOT HUMAN ANY MORE!
ONE DAY THEY'RE GOING TO COME
AND TRY TO KILL US!
SHOW THE ENEMY NO MERCY!
BUT YOU DO HAVE AN OPTION...
I COULD TAKE OVER AGAIN.
ARE YOU JUST GOING TO
CLOSE YOUR EYES
TO WHAT YOU DON'T WANT TO DO
AND THEN SAY YOU DID NOTHING
WRONG AFTER IT'S ALL OVER?
I'M WILLING TO KILL THEM....
I DON'T CARE ABOUT
ANYONE ELSE!
I FIGHT TO
ENSURE MY OWN SURVIVAL!
I'M NOT LIKE YOU!
THEN WHY DID YOU COME HERE?
I CAME HERE BECAUSE I'M A
MEMBER OF CELESTIAL BEING.
NO, YOU CAME HERE TO KILL.
I DIDN'T! I CAME HERE
AS A GUNDAM MEISTER!
YOU'RE KILLING PEOPLE BECAUSE
IT'S YOUR JOB?
AT LEAST PULL THE
TRIGGER WITH YOUR OWN EMOTIONS!
PULL IT FOR YOURSELF!
AND DO IT WITHOUT MERCY!
I DON'T WANT TO SHOOT...
ALLELUJAH!
I DON'T WANT TO SHOOT!
(Screaming)
(Screaming maniacally)
(Boom)
(Hallelujah laughing)
GOOD WORK!
THAT WAS NICELY DONE,
MY OTHER SELF!
THINGS ARE SURE
GOING TO GET INTERESTING.
THE SENSORS ARE PICKING UP
KYRIOS AND VIRTUE RETURNING.
THE MISSION'S COMPLETE.
CHRISTINA, GO AHEAD AND
LEAK THE INFORMATION
ABOUT THE SUPER
SOLDIER INSTITUTE
TO THE MEDIA AS PLANNED.
ROGER THAT.
I CAN'T BELIEVE THE HRL
WAS REBUILDING ITS
SOLDIERS' BODIES.
THIS'LL BE A
MONSTER SCANDAL!
STOP THAT!
ALLELUJAH...
Sergei:
APPARENTLY CELESTIAL BEING
ATTACKED QUANQIU.
THEY TARGETED THE SUPER
SOLDIER INSTITUTE YOU BELONG TO.
HUH?
THEY... THEY WHAT?
AN ATTACK ON A FACILITY
THAT WAS A SECRET EVEN TO ME.
ONE OF THE GUNDAM
PILOTS HAD TO BE
FROM THE
SUPER SOLDIER INSTITUTE...
AND YOU KNEW ABOUT THAT,
DIDN'T YOU?
AM I WRONG?
NO, I...I HAD NO IDEA.
I'M USING MY AUTHORITY TO
CLOSE DOWN THIS FACILITY.
(Gasps)
AND YOU'LL BE THOROUGHLY
INTERROGATED.
I'M... I'M GOING TO BE WHAT?
JUST A MINUTE HERE!
THE WHOLE SORRY INCIDENT
HAS ALREADY BEEN LEAKED
TO THE WORLD.
YOU FAILED
TO REPORT THIS PROPERLY
FORCING US INTO AN
UNFAVORABLE SITUATION.
YOUR CRIMES
ARE VERY GRAVE.
TAKE HIM AWAY.
HUH?
CELESTIAL BEING IS GOING TO GET
A LOT OF CREDIT FOR THIS...
COLONEL SMIRNOV.
STILL ON STANDBY, LIEUTENANT.
GET BACK TO YOUR STATION.
SIR.
(Sighs)
WHAT CAN I DO FOR YOU,
ALLELUJAH?
HAVE YOU COME UP
WITH A NEW MISSION?
MISS SUMERAGI...CAN I
HAVE A GLASS OF THAT, TOO?
AND THE REASON?
I JUST REALLY WANT ONE.
BUT YOU'RE NOT OLD ENOUGH
YET. I'D BE BREAKING THE LAW.
BUT WE'RE ALREADY
NOTORIOUS TERRORISTS.
NEVERTHELESS, I CAN'T
GIVE YOU A DRINK.
BUT IT'S OKAY NOW.
HUH?
ACCORDING TO
GREENWICH MEAN TIME...
I JUST CAME OF AGE
A FEW MINUTES AGO...
IS THAT SO...
(Clink)
THIS MIGHT SOUND STRANGE
UNDER THE CIRCUMSTANCES,
BUT HERE'S TO YOU.
THANKS FOR THE
BIRTHDAY WISH.
(Gulping)
WHY DRINK SOMETHING
SO BITTER?
(Chuckles)
YOU'LL KNOW SOON ENOUGH,
I'M SURE OF IT.
(Engines roar)
♪
Narrator:
A CIVIL WAR
BREAKS OUT IN AZADISTAN,
AND SETSUNA IS SENT
TO HIS HOMELAND.
WHAT IS THE CONDEMNATION
HE RECEIVES THERE?
NEXT EPISODE:
"TO THE LIMITS OF
HOLY TEACHINGS".
BEHIND HOPE,
DESPAIR CAN SNEAK IN.