YOU CAN DIE NOW.
(Screams in extreme pain)
HOW DO YOU LIKE THE TASTE
OF THE AGRISSA'S PLASMA FIELD?!
NOW, YOU'RE GOING TO DIE AND
LEAVE YOUR MACHINE BEHIND
YOU LITTLE KRUGIS PUNK!
(Screams in pain)
Setsuna: (weakly)
GUN... DAM...
(Grunts)
WHAT THE...?!
(Struggling gasps)
IS THAT...?
WHAT THE HELL?
Setsuna:
GUN... DAM...
(Screams)
GUNDAM!
Nena:
YOU STILL ALIVE?
♪
HEY, EXIA PILOT,
ARE YOU OKAY IN THERE?
WHO ARE YOU?
NENA TRINITY.
AND I'M JUST LIKE YOU,
I'M A REAL GUNDAM MEISTER!
YOU'RE ANOTHER GUNDAM MEISTER?
AND WHAT'S YOUR MACHINE?
(Giggles)
GUNDAM THRONE UNIT THREE,
THRONE DREI.
Setsuna:
UNIT THREE?
THAT'S RIGHT, MY BIG BROS ARE
THE PILOTS OF UNITS ONE AND TWO.
AND RIGHT ABOUT NOW...
Patrick:
ALL MACHINES,
STAY IN FORMATION.
WE'RE TAKING THE GUNDAM
BACK TO HQ LIKE THIS.
AND I, PATRICK COLASOUR,
WAS IN CHARGE OF EVERYTHING.
THAT'S RIGHT,
IF I CAN CAPTURE A GUNDAM
THEN SURELY THE COLONEL'S HEART
WILL BE NEXT.
(Beeps)
HUH?
(Startled yelp)
(Screams)
WHAT NOW?
Johann:
TARGETED HELLION TEAM,
CONFIRMED DESTROYED.
CONTINUING MISSION.
THAT LIGHT MEANS IT'S...
Sergei:
ALL MACHINES, DON'T LET
YOUR GUARD DOWN!
THE WINGED ONE
COULD GO WILD ON US AGAIN!
Soldiers: (together)
ROGER!
ROGER THAT!
(Thinking)
THIS IS THE GUNDAM
THAT ATTACKED
THE SUPER HUMAN INSTITUTE
AND KILLED MY COMRADES.
BUT WHY? YOU'RE ONE OF US.
(Gasps)
WHAT'S THIS PRESSURE
I'M FEELING?
Sergei:
ENEMY ATTACK!?
WHAT KIND OF WEAPON
IS THIS?
THESE THINGS AREN'T MISSILES!
Sergei:
THE OTHER TEAMS FAILED
TO INTERCEPT THEM?!
(Tense gasp)
Peries:
THAT'S THE MACHINE THERE!
Michael:
GUNDAM THRONE UNIT TWO,
THRONE ZWEI!
MICHAEL TRINITY!
EXTERMINATING!
FLY, MY FANGS!
Sergei:
(Aggressive yell)
COLONEL!
(Peries grunts)
(Michael chuckles)
YOU'RE WEAK! SO EASY TO BREAK!
Graham:
WHAT THE...
WE'RE UNDER ATTACK!
Daryl:
RANDY'S DOWN!
Howard:
HERE COMES ANOTHER ONE!
Graham:
STUART!
SCATTER!
WITH THAT KIND OF RANGE,
WE'RE NOT DEALING WITH
A NORMAL WEAPON HERE!
I DIDN'T THINK THEY HAD ANY MORE
OF THOSE DAMNED MACHINES!
NO ONE TOLD US. GUNDAMS!
DAMN!
Graham:
OUR FORMATION'S BEEN
TORN TO PIECES.
WE'RE FALLING BACK!
ROGER THAT!
(Groans)
WHO WAS THAT?
Lockon:
WHAT IS THAT MACHINE?
HARO! YOU KNOW WHAT IT IS?
NO DATA!
(Beeps)
LOOKS LIKE I MADE IT
JUST IN THE NICK OF TIME.
HUH?
WHO ARE YOU?
I AM THE GUNDAM MEISTER
OF THRONE EINS,
JOHANN TRINITY.
YOUR NAME'S JOHANN TRINITY?
THERE ARE ACTUALLY
THREE OF US
BUT MY BROTHER AND SISTER
HAVE ALREADY HEADED OUT
TO RESCUE YOUR FELLOW MEISTERS.
Lockon:
WHAT DO YOU MEAN?
Nena:
JOHANN!
AH, NENA.
Nena:
I'VE COMPLETED MY MISSION HERE!
Johann:
I SEE.
NENA, DISPERSE GN PARTICLES
OVER MAXIMUM AREA.
WE WANT TO LEAVE
THIS AIRSPACE AT ONCE.
ROGER THAT, JOHANN!
LET'S GO, HARO!
WHATEVER!
GN PARTICLES!
MAXIMUM DISPERSAL!
GO!
STEALTH FIELD!
ALL THAT LIGHT...
THERE'S SO MUCH!
ARE THOSE ACTUALLY GN PARTICLES?
WHAT... WHAT'S GOING ON HERE?
(Chuckles)
THAT'S OUR NENA!
THE DISPERSAL AREA IS HUGE!
THREE NEW GUNDAMS
JUST APPEARED OUT OF NOWHERE?
YES, MA'AM!
IT APPEARS THAT BECAUSE OF
THE ENEMY'S NEW REINFORCEMENTS,
WE FAILED
TO CAPTURE THE GUNDAMS!
THEY FAILED?
HOW COULD THIS HAPPEN?
COLONEL!
YES, WHAT IS IT?!
MA'AM, I'M SEEING
A DRAMATIC INCREASE
IN THE CUT OFF POINTS
FOR THE COMM LINKS!
(Angry grunt)
WHAT'S THIS ALL ABOUT?
ARE YOU SAYING
THOSE NEW MACHINES
HAVE THE ABILITY TO SCATTER
THOSE SPECIAL PARTICLES
OVER A MUCH LARGER AREA?
Operator:
WITH ALL THIS,
THE ONLY WAY WE CAN FIND
THE GUNDAMS IS WITH OUR EYES!
I KNOW THAT!
THIS IS CAPTAIN GRAHAM AKER
OF THE OVER FLAGS.
WE FAILED TO CAPTURE THE GUNDAM.
WE NEED REINFORCEMENTS‐‐
(Static)
OUR COMMUNICATIONS.
(Gasps)
THE PARTICLES!
Sergei:
THE COMMUNICATION CUT OFF AREA
IS INCREASING?
IF THEY ALWAYS HAD
THIS ABILITY,
WHY DIDN'T
THEY DO IT BEFORE NOW?
WHAT ARE YOU UP TO,
CELESTIAL BEING?
Patrick:
HQ, CAN YOU HEAR ME?
THIS IS PATRICK!
PLEASE RESPOND!
(Static)
DAMN IT, I CAN'T GET THROUGH.
HOW THE HELL AM I GOING TO
GET BACK TO BASE NOW?
(Yelling)
COLONEL!
Christina:
(Gasps)
IT'S A CODED MESSAGE
FROM HARO!
ALL FOUR GUNDAMS MADE IT!
THEY'RE GOING TO
RENDEZVOUS
AT THE NUMBER SIX SPOT
IN THE PACIFIC!
THAT'S INCREDIBLE!
THEY SURE HAD US WORRIED,
ALRIGHT!
AND ALL OF THEM...
MISSION COMPLETE,
MISS SUMERAGI!
HOW WONDERFUL!
YES, BUT HOW?
WHAT?
NO, IT'S OKAY,
IT'S NOTHING!
SOMETIMES IT'S A GOOD THING
WHEN YOUR FORECASTS
DON'T COME TRUE.
WHO COULD'VE IMAGINED THAT GROUP
WOULD HAVE
THREE MORE NEW GUNDAMS
THEY COULD DEPLOY.
IS IT POSSIBLE CELESTIAL BEING
ACTUALLY SAW THROUGH OUR PLAN
AND SET THIS WHOLE AFFAIR UP?
SEVEN GUNDAMS NOW.
SO THERE ARE THREE
NEW GUNDAMS.
DAMN IT.
NO ONE SAID ANYTHING.
WHAT KIND OF MACHINES
WERE THEY FLYING?
THOSE MACHINES...THEY AREN'T
A PART OF VEDA'S OPERATION PLAN.
WHAT KIND OF GUNDAMS ARE THEY?!
(Loud yawn)
WHAT'S WRONG WITH YOU,
SAJI?
YOU'VE BEEN LIKE,
YAWNING ALL DAY.
THEY WERE RUNNING CONSTANT
UPDATES ALL NIGHT
ABOUT CELESTIAL BEING AND
HOW THEY PERFORMED
AN ARMED INTERVENTION
DURING THAT BIG JOINT
MILITARY EXERCISE IN THE DESERT.
I WATCHED ALL NIGHT
AND THEN
BEFORE I KNEW IT,
IT WAS MORNING.
OH. THAT SOUNDS
INTERESTING.
YOU DON'T THINK
THIS IS A BIG DEAL?
I'M MORE WORRIED ABOUT
THE EXAMS THAT BEGIN TOMORROW.
(Despondent)
OH, THAT'S RIGHT.
(Footsteps)
Alejandro:
OBSERVER ALEJANDRO CORNER.
J4:
THESE EMERGENCY MEETINGS
ARE SO UNSETTLING.
D3:
I'M GUESSING THIS IS
ABOUT THE TAKLAMAKAN REGION
AND THE THREE NEW GUNDAMS
THAT APPEARED THERE.
S8:
THERE DOESN'T SEEM TO BE
ANY MENTION OF THESE MACHINES
IN VEDA'S PLANS.
C5:
WE CAN OBVIOUSLY DEDUCE
FROM THIS THAT CELESTIAL BEING
HAS A SECRET SECOND TEAM.
I WISH TO MAKE A PROPOSAL
TO ALL THE ESTEEMED OBSERVERS.
IT CONCERNS WHETHER
WE SHOULD ACCEPT OR REJECT
THE THREE
NEWLY ACTIVATED GUNDAMS.
N1:
YOU'RE PUSHING FOR
A DECISION TOO QUICKLY.
T2:
BEFORE WE DO THAT,
I BELIEVE WE SHOULD RE‐EXAMINE
CELESTIAL BEING'S ACTIVITIES
AND THE RESULTS THAT HAVE BEEN
ACHIEVED UP UNTIL NOW.
L9:
I SUPPORT THAT SUGGESTION.
V7:
AS DO I.
VERY WELL, THEN.
Alejandro:
CELESTIAL BEING'S
FIRST MISSION
BEGAN WITH
AN ARMED INTERVENTION
AT THE OFFICIAL UNVEILING OF
THE AEU'S NEWEST MOBILE SUIT,
THE ENACT.
240082 EXIA HAS TARGET
LOCATION IN SIGHT.
CEASE GN PARTICLE DISPERSAL
UPON ARRIVAL AT TARGET.
ALRIGHT, WHO THE HELL ARE YOU?
FROM THE UNION?
HUMAN REFORM LEAGUE?
WELL, EITHER WAY,
YOU'RE A PARTY‐CRASHER
AND YOU WEREN'T INVITED.
Patrick:
AND NOW YOU'RE GOING
TO PAY THE PRICE!
ONCE THE EXIA
ARRIVED ON THE SCENE
IT COMPLETELY OVERWHELMED
THE ENACT,
BOTH DEMONSTRATING
ITS SUPERIOR CAPABILITIES
AND DELAYING DEPLOYMENT OF
THE NEW ENEMY MOBILE SUIT.
LATER, EXIA,
TOGETHER WITH DYNAMES,
REVEALED TO THE WORLD
THAT THE AEU HAD STATIONED
MORE MILITARY FORCES IN
ITS ORBITAL ELEVATOR
THAN WAS ALLOWED
BY TREATY LIMITATIONS.
IT'S LOCKON.
IMMEDIATELY FOLLOWING THIS,
KYRIOS AND VIRTUE CARRIED OUT
A MISSION IN WHICH
THEY PREVENTED A TERRORIST
ATTACK ON HEAVEN'S PILLAR,
THE HUMAN REFORM LEAGUE'S
ORBITAL ELEVATOR.
J4:
WHAT WAS THE POINT
OF THIS MISSION?
N1:
I'D SAY THAT, BY PREVENTING
A TERRORIST ATTACK
RATHER THAN ENGAGING IN
CONFLICT INTERVENTION,
THEY WERE SEEKING
THE WORLD'S ACCEPTANCE
AND UNDERSTANDING.
Aeolia:
I WOULD LIKE TO ADDRESS
THIS STATEMENT
TO EVERY SINGLE HUMAN BEING
BORN AND RAISED ON EARTH.
WE CALL OURSELVES
SIMPLY CELESTIAL BEING.
WE ARE A PRIVATE ARMED
ORGANIZATION
IN POSSESSION
OF THE MOBILE WEAPON GUNDAM.
Alejandro:
AND THEN, THE FOUNDER AND
CREATOR OF CELESTIAL BEING,
AEOLIA SCHENBERG,
BROADCAST A STATEMENT THAT WAS
SEEN AROUND THE WORLD.
THUS, A PLAN THAT WAS
TWO CENTURIES IN THE MAKING
HAD REACHED THE MOMENT WHERE
IT COULD BE SET IN MOTION.
T2:
THE SECOND MISSION
WAS AN ARMED INTERVENTION
INTO THE ETHNIC CONFLICT ON
THE ISLAND OF CEYLON,
FORMERLY KNOWN AS SRI LANKA.
L9:
THIS CONFLICT WAS WORSENING
BECAUSE THE HUMAN REFORM LEAGUE
BECAME INVOLVED
IN AN ATTEMPT TO GUARANTEE
THE SECURITY OF THEIR SOLAR
ENERGY TRANSMISSION TUBES.
Alejandro:
AFTER THAT,
THE GUNDAMS WERE DEPLOYED IN
DIFFERENT TEAM COMBINATIONS
IN ORDER TO COMPLETE
A VARIETY OF MISSIONS,
ALL ACCORDING TO THE PLANS
RECOMMENDED BY VEDA.
(Metal clashing)
YOU'RE MISTAKEN!
Michael:
THINGS HAD BEEN GOING PRETTY
SMOOTHLY UP TO THAT POINT.
THEN THERE WAS TARIBIA,
THE SOUTH AMERICAN REPUBLIC
WHERE THEY DECIDED TO PERFORM
AN ARMED INTERVENTION.
AMERICA AND TARIBIA
WERE PLAYING SOME GAME
AND THEY GOT
CAUGHT IN THE MIDDLE.
SEE, IF IT HAD BEEN ME
I WOULD HAVE BEATEN THE CRAP
OUT OF BOTH OF THOSE ARMIES.
YOU'RE SO EXTREME,
MICHAEL.
YES, BUT FOR THEM,
THEIR PLANS
WOULD SOON BE PLAGUED
BY A NUMBER OF ABERRATIONS.
D3:
KYRIOS'S RESCUE WORK WAS NOT
PART OF THAT MISSION.
N1: IT WAS REPORTED THAT THE
PILOT, ALLELUJAH HAPTISM,
TOOK INDEPENDENT ACTION
IN THAT MATTER.
C5:
AND THIS UNEXPECTED COURSE
OF ACTION RESULTED IN
DYNAMES REVEALING ITS HIGH
ALTITUDE FIRING CAPABILITY.
TARGETED AND FIRING!
V7:
THIS FORCED VEDA
TO MAKE REVISIONS
TO ITS OPERATION PLAN IN
THE FOLLOWING DAYS.
AND THEN STILL ANOTHER
UNBELIEVABLE INCIDENT
TOOK PLACE DURING THE ARMED
INTERVENTION IN MORALIA.
Johann:
EXIA'S PILOT OPENED
HIS COCKPIT HATCH
AND DELIBERATELY
REVEALED HIMSELF TO THE ENEMY.
WHAT THE HELL?
Nena:
(Giggles)
HOW STUPID CAN A PERSON BE?!
Michael:
SWEET! HE'S EVEN CRAZIER
THAN I AM!
DYNAMES.
S8:
WHY WOULD HE DO THAT?
V7:
THE PILOT,
SETSUNA F. SEIEI,
REFUSED TO FILE
A MISSION REPORT.
J4:
HOWEVER, THE MISSION ITSELF
WAS COMPLETED.
THERE WERE
THOSE WHO RECOMMENDED
REMOVING SETSUNA F. SEIEI,
SINCE HE WAS THE SOURCE
OF THE PROBLEM,
BUT SINCE A UNANIMOUS DECISION
COULDN'T BE REACHED,
THE ISSUE WAS DROPPED.
D3:
YES, UNLESS WE ALL ARE
OF THE SAME OPINION
WE CANNOT EXERCISE OUR VETO.
(Giggles)
N1:
AND THEN, AS PREDICTED,
THE WORLD BEGAN SHOWING
SIGNS OF RESISTANCE.
(Laughs)
(Gasps)
(Glass shatters)
L9:
DEMANDING THAT CELESTIAL BEING
CEASE ITS ACTIVITIES,
A TERRORIST NETWORK BEGAN
A CAMPAIGN OF
INDISCRIMINATE RETALIATION.
Saji:
THE... THE BUS!
(Gasps in horror)
Man:
THE BUS JUST EXPLODED!
TERRORISTS!
A TERRORIST ATTACK!
A CODED MESSAGE FROM THE NRO?
AND THE BND
AND DGSE, TOO.
CLEARLY IT'S A MESSAGE
FROM THE WORLD.
C5:
THANKS TO THE ASSISTANCE
OF THE WORLD'S
INTELLIGENCE AGENCIES,
THE MATTER WAS QUICKLY
DEALT WITH.
D3:
WHETHER THEY LIKE IT OR NOT,
THERE'S NO DOUBT THE WORLD
HAS COME TO ACKNOWLEDGE
THE EXISTENCE OF CELESTIAL
BEING AS A REAL ISSUE.
Alejandro:
HOWEVER,
THE MAJOR POWERS WERE NOT QUITE
AS WILLING TO ACCEPT THEM.
THE HUMAN REFORM LEAGUE CREATED
THE CHOBU SPECIAL FORCES TEAM
AND LAUNCHED AN ATTACK
ON THE PTOLEMAIOS,
CELESTIAL BEING'S
MULTI‐PURPOSE TRANSPORT.
Sergei:
NUMBER THREE,
DON'T FORGET YOU'RE TRACKING
THE THIRD COMMUNICATION
CUTOFF POINT.
DYNAMES, OPEN FIRE!
Lockon:
I'M ON IT!
(Grunts)
N1:
BUT IN ACTUALITY,
THEY WERE LESS INTERESTED IN
ATTACKING THE PTOLEMAIOS,
THAN THEY WERE
IN CAPTURING A GUNDAM.
L9:
ALLELUJAH HAPTISM,
A FORMER TEST SUBJECT
OF THE SUPER HUMAN INSTITUTE,
WAS AFFECTED BY
QUANTUM BRAIN WAVES.
HE NEARLY ALLOWED THE KYRIOS
TO BE CAPTURED.
S8:
ALSO, IN A DESPERATE BID
TO ESCAPE,
VIRTUE WAS FORCED TO REVEAL
THE GN‐004 GUNDAM NADLEEH
TO THE ENEMY.
A MOST ESSENTIAL SYSTEM INDEED.
(Metal clashing)
T2:
THE SAME COULD BE SAID
ABOUT KYRIOS.
WE WEREN'T READY TO SHOW
THE ENEMY THAT WEAPON JUST YET.
NO, STOP!
STOP IT, PLEASE!
(Screaming)
J4:
ON THAT ISSUE, THERE WAS
SOME CONCERN EXPRESSED OVER
THE ABILITIES OF
THE TACTICAL FORECASTER,
SUMERAGI LEE NORIEGA.
AS WITH THE MATTER OF
SETSUNA F. SEIEI,
THOSE OPINIONS WERE
NOT UNANIMOUS
AND SO IT WAS PASSED OVER.
D3:
WHY WAS THE MATTER CONCERNING
ALLELUJAH HAPTISM PASSED OVER?
S8:
OH THAT. IT'S BECAUSE
HE SUBMITTED A MISSION PLAN
THAT INCLUDED THE LOCATION
AND DESTRUCTION OF
THE SUPER HUMAN INSTITUTE'S
LABORATORY.
C5:
NEVERTHELESS,
HE REMAINS SUSCEPTIBLE
TO QUANTUM BRAIN WAVES.
THIS COULD BE
A PROBLEM IN FUTURE MISSIONS.
T2:
I BELIEVE THERE'S
ENOUGH REASON TO CONSIDER
WHETHER OR NOT WE SHOULD
KEEP HIM AS A GUNDAM MEISTER.
(Allelujah screaming)
IN OTHER WORDS,
THEIR STYLE IS JUST
A LITTLE TOO SOFT FOR THE JOB.
BESIDES, I DON'T LIKE THEIR
SILLY HABIT OF NOT KILLING
THE ENEMY PILOTS THEY FIGHT
UNLESS THEY ABSOLUTELY HAVE TO.
IT'D ONLY HELP US
IN THE LONG RUN
IF THE NUMBER OF EXPERIENCED
PILOTS OUT THERE WERE REDUCED.
DON'T YOU AGREE,
JOHANN?
DON'T BE SO HARD ON THEM,
MICHAEL.
THEY'RE JUST MORE
CONCERNED ABOUT
HOW THE PUBLIC PERCEIVES THEM.
THAT'S MY POINT!
THAT'S WHAT MAKES 'EM SO SOFT!
FIRST THEY PICK A FIGHT
WITH THE WHOLE WORLD AND THEN
THEY'RE WORRIED ABOUT HURTING
EVERYONE'S FEELINGS!
YOU KNOW, I CAN'T STAND
WISHY‐WASHY MEN.
THAT'S RIGHT!
FOR INSTANCE, TAKE A LOOK AT
THAT MESS IN AZADISTAN.
Setsuna:
THIS TIME...
YOU HAVE MY THANKS
FOR THIS.
PLEASE HURRY.
(Gasps)
PRINCESS!
IT'S TOO DANGEROUS!
MARINA ISMAIL,
WHAT HAPPENS NEXT WILL DETERMINE
WHETHER WE COME BACK OR NOT.
Michael:
WAS THAT LIKE NON‐VIOLENT
RESISTANCE?
THAT CRAP THAT WAS POPULAR
A LONG TIME AGO?
WHAT'S HE DOING IN
A GUNDAM THEN?
L9:
AND NOW, TO THE MATTER
IN THE TAKLAMAKAN REGION.
V7:
VEDA'S REPORT IS INCOMPLETE,
BUT IF THE SECOND TEAM
HADN'T APPEARED
THERE'S A HIGH PROBABILITY
THE GUNDAMS
WOULD'VE BEEN CAPTURED.
J4:
I CONCUR.
N1:
BUT WHERE WERE
THE SECOND TEAM'S GUNDAM'S
SOLAR REACTORS MADE?
THERE SHOULD ONLY BE
FIVE OF THESE REACTORS
ACTIVE RIGHT NOW.
T2:
CONCERNING THAT ISSUE,
I'M SURE VEDA WILL BE GIVING US
PRECISE INFORMATION SOON.
C5:
BUT THAT MEANS
THERE IS INFORMATION
WE ARE NOT PRIVY TO.
S8:
IT'S OF NO CONCERN.
WE ARE JUST OBSERVERS.
REGARDLESS OF
WHAT THE WORLD DOES,
WE CAN ONLY EXERCISE OUR VETO
OVER CELESTIAL BEING
BY REACHING A CONSENSUS.
NOW THAT WE'VE HAD A CHANCE
TO EXPRESS OUR VIEWS,
I WANT TO ASK YOU ALL
ONCE AGAIN.
SHOULD WE OBSERVERS ACCEPT
THE THREE NEW GUNDAMS AND
THEIR SUBSEQUENT ACTIONS OR NOT?
V7:
I WILL ACKNOWLEDGE THEM.
L9:
I ACCEPT THEM.
D3:
I AGREE.
(The other observers agree)
SO BE IT.
WE'RE NOT FAR FROM
THE RENDEZVOUS POINT NOW.
SO, DO YOU THINK
THEY'LL SHOW UP, JOHANN?
THEY COULD BE AFRAID
OF US, YOU KNOW!
OH NO, THEY WILL BE THERE.
IF THEY REALLY ARE
GUNDAM MEISTERS,
THEY'LL BE CURIOUS
AND THEY'LL WANT TO LEARN
EVERYTHING THEY CAN ABOUT US
AND THE GUNDAM THRONES.
(Excited gasp)
I SEE THEM!
Johann:
(chuckles)
THEN LET US GO AND GREET THEM,
OUR FELLOW GUNDAM MEISTERS.
ALL RIGHT.
ROGER THAT!
♪
Narrator:
WHEN TEAM TRINITY COMMENCES
ITS ARMED INTERVENTION,
THE WORLD SHAKES AND TREMBLES
BEFORE ITS FIERCE ASSAULT.
NEXT EPISODE:
"ASSAULT OF THE THRONES".
AMBITION HIDDEN BY IDEALS
REARS ITS HEAD.