(Motor running)
Operator #15A:
TWO‐WAY COMM SYSTEMS
HAVE BEEN
PLACED AT ALL
DESIGNATED POINTS!
Operator #15B:
MESSAGE FROM EURO‐TWO,
"NOW COMMENCING
DISTRIBUTION
OF AIRBORNE TWO‐WAY
COMM SYSTEMS."
Operator #15C:
FROM UNION‐THREE,
COMMUNICATIONS NET RECEPTION
STATUS IS ALL GREEN.
Operator #15D:
SIMULATION PLAN,
ALL CLEAR.
Operator #15E:
ALL TEAMS PARTICIPATING IN
THE EXERCISE
ARE FULLY LINKED
TO THE COMMUNICATIONS NET.
SIGNAL STRENGTH FOR ALL
MOBILE SUITS IS SATISFACTORY.
IT'S HARD TO
BELIEVE...
I NEVER THOUGHT WE'D
JOIN FORCES
WITH THE
UNION AND THE AEU.
Sergei:
LIKE IT'S ONE BIG PARTY.
Kati:
LIEUTENANT, HOW'S YOUR
DUST‐PROOFING HOLDING UP?
IT'S DOING JUST FINE,
COLONEL!
WATCH ME GO TO WORK!
CAPTURING A GUNDAM WILL
BE A SNAP WITH THIS!
IMPOSSIBLE.
OH, COME ON!
OVER FLAGS ARE TO REMAIN
ON STANDBY UNTIL ORDERED.
Graham:
ROGER THAT.
52 TEAMS IN TOTAL...
832 MOBILE SUITS
PARTICIPATING.
YOU MAY CALL US COWARDS
FOR THIS...
BUT I'LL FOLLOW THE MILITARY'S
PLAN ON THIS ONE...GUNDAMS.
♪
HMM...
LOUISE, HOW MUCH LONGER
ARE YOU GOING TO BE LIKE THIS?
I'M DEPRESSED BECAUSE
MOM WENT HOME.
I KNOW THAT.
PLEASE CHEER ME UP.
CHEER UP, LOUISE‐‐
I MEAN, BUY ME THINGS!
PLEASE.
HUH?
I CAN'T BUY THOSE, LOUISE!
I CAN'T AFFORD BRAND‐NAME
ITEMS LIKE THAT!
(Growling)
SAJI, I WANT YOU
TO BUY THEM FOR ME!
I CAN'T.
BUY THEM,
BUY THEM, BUY THEM!
WHAT ARE THOSE
KIDS UP TO?
SO INNOCENT
AND PEACEFUL,
AND WITH NEARLY
A THOUSAND MOBILE SUITS
GETTING READY TO TAKE PART
IN A HUGE EXERCISE.
I WISH EVERYONE
WAS THAT PEACEFUL.
(Sighs)
(Thinking):
I WONDER, WAS THIS
GIGANTIC EXERCISE
IN YOUR PLANS, TOO...
AEOLIA SCHENBERG?
Chairman:
HOW IS EVERYTHING
PROGRESSING?
WE'VE JUST RECEIVED A
REPORT FROM INTELLIGENCE.
THE LATEST UPDATE HAS THREE
MOBILE SUITS
AND THREE PERSONNEL
TRANSPORTS HEADING FOR
THE URANIUM STORAGE
FACILITY.
NOW IF ONLY OUR TRUE QUARRY
WOULD GET CAUGHT IN THE NET.
VERY WELL THEN.
IT SEEMS THE TWO WAY
COMMUNICATION SYSTEM HAS
DETECTED SOME "INTERFERENCE"
AT THE EXERCISE GROUND.
AS WE EXPECTED. ADVISE THE
COMMANDER TO CHANGE
THE OPERATION ACCORDINGLY.
WE WERE THE ONES WHO
PROVIDED THIS SITE,
IN THE FACE OF
STRONG PUBLIC CRITICISM.
WE WANT AT LEAST TWO
MACHINES IN RETURN.
(Engine roaring)
Lockon:
ALLELUJAH... KEEP YOUR
SPEED AND ALTITUDE STEADY.
(Gasps)
WOULD YOU STOP ROCKING US?
LOOK, YOU'RE
ASKING A BIT MUCH!
Captain #15A:
OBSERVATION TEAMS,
WHAT IS THE GUNDAMS' TARGET?
SIR, WE HAVE NO UNITS
ALONG THE ROUTE
WHERE WE HAVE
COMM INTERFERENCE.
Kati:
WHAT?
THE GUNDAMS ARE HEADING
STRAIGHT FOR THE
SITE WHERE
THE ENRICHED
URANIUM IS BURIED.
Sergei:
WHAT THE HELL IS THIS?
HOW COULD WE MISS A
GROUP OF TERRORISTS
HEADED STRAIGHT FOR
THE FACILITY?
COLONEL, WE JUST RECEIVED
ORDERS FROM HEADQUARTERS
TO CAPTURE THE GUNDAMS.
(Groans)
I SEE... SO, THIS WAS
ALL JUST A SETUP.
(Cannons fire)
(Boom)
Sergei:
THE GOVERNMENT KNEW WHAT
THE TERRORISTS WERE UP TO...
AND PURPOSELY LEFT THEM ALONE
TO LURE THE GUNDAMS OUT.
DYNAMES HERE.
TARGETED AND READY TO FIRE!
(Boom)
(Bang)
(Crash)
(Boom)
ALL SHOTS ON TARGET!
LET'S GET GOING,
ALLELUJAH!
ROGER!
(Beeping)
HMM?
(Missiles flying)
IT'S AN ENEMY ATTACK!
(Yelling)
ENEMIES APPROACHING!
DAMN IT...
LOCKON!
I KNOW!
(Boom)
(Yelling)
ALLELUJAH!
ENEMIES APPROACHING!
WHAT THE...
WHO ARE THESE GUYS?
LOCKON!
I'M OKAY.
WE'VE GOT INCOMING!
Soldier #15A:
MAINTAIN THE BARRAGE.
KEEP THOSE GUNDAMS
PINNED DOWN!
(Boom)
(Coffee dripping)
WE JUST PASSED
THE SCHEDULED
COMPLETION TIME
FOR THE FIRST PHASE.
I JUST HOPE EVERYBODY MADE IT
OUT OF THERE IN ONE PIECE.
WHAT'S YOUR FORECAST,
MISS SUMERAGI?
I THINK THEY'VE PROBABLY
SWITCHED TO PLAN B2 BY NOW.
IT'S TIME
FOR EXIA AND VIRTUE.
SUCCESSFUL FIRST ATTACK
FOR UNION THREE.
WE HAVE TWO
GUNDAMS AT TF‐4122.
CONTINUE LONG‐RANGE
BOMBARDMENT!
ROGER! CONTINUING
LONG‐RANGE BOMBARDMENT!
GETTING A VISUAL SIGNAL
FROM HUMAN‐ONE!
THEY REQUEST A TEAM BE
DISPATCHED TO POINT TF‐2123!
SO, THEY'RE CHOOSING THE
WEAKEST AREAS TO ATTACK.
DEPLOY THE TWENTY‐THIRD
MOBILE SUIT TEAM IMMEDIATELY!
Operator #15C:
TWENTY‐THIRD MOBILE SUIT
TEAM MOVE OUT!
TWENTY‐THIRD
MOBILE SUIT TEAM MOVE OUT!
COLONEL! HOW AM I
SUPPOSED TO CAPTURE
ONE OF THOSE GUNDAMS
FOR YOU IF YOU WON'T EVEN
GIVE ME THE ORDER
TO LAUNCH?
STANDBY FOR NOW.
COLONEL!
JUST TRUST ME. I'LL MAKE
A MAN OUT OF YOU YET.
UH...
PREPARE TO SWITCH OVER
TO MISSION PLAN B2.
ROGER THAT. EXIA, DISSOLVE
EXTERNAL CAMOUFLAGE MEMBRANE.
I AM NOW COMMENCING MISSION.
Pilot #15A:
I SEE TWO GUNDAMS!
NOTIFY HEADQUARTERS!
(Slash)
♪
THIS IS VIRTUE. IN POSITION
TO SECURE ESCAPE ROUTE.
GN BAZOOKA... BURST MODE.
PARTICLE COMPRESSION
RATE AT 97 PERCENT.
GN PARTICLES...NOW RELEASING.
(Boom)
(Whoosh)
IT'S TIERIA!
THE OTHERS HAVE SWITCHED
TO PLAN B2.
WE'VE GOT TO
GET OUT OF HERE, ALLELUJAH!
ROGER!
FIRST SHOT COMPLETE.
NOW COMMENCING GN
PARTICLE RECHARGE.
THERE'RE SO MANY OF THEM!
A RESPONSE ALREADY?
Lichtendahl:
TWO HOURS SINCE
IT ALL BEGAN.
Christina:
IF THEY'RE ON PLAN B2...
DYNAMES AND KYRIOS SHOULD REACH
THE RENDEZVOUS POINT
PRETTY SOON.
IF WE COULD AT LEAST USE
THE GN ARMS, THEN MAYBE...
BY THIS TIME THEY
SHOULD HAVE SWITCHED OVER
FROM PLAN B2 TO E5.
WHICH MEANS THAT MACHINE
IS GOING TO BE SHOWING UP.
ALLELUJAH...
(Screams)
(Screaming)
ALLELUJAH, WHAT'S WRONG?
MY HEAD IS KILLING ME...
(Screams)
SHE'S COMING...
THE SUPER‐SOLDIER.
(Moaning)
THE SUPER‐SOLDIER?
YOU MEAN THE HRL MACHINE
FROM YOUR REPORT?
ENEMIES APPROACHING!
(Engines roaring)
IT'S HER!
(Gasps)
ALLELUJAH!
WE FELL INTO THEIR TRAP!
(Screaming)
(Missiles ricocheting)
TIERIA! HOW LONG TILL
YOU'RE RECHARGED?
ANOTHER 170.
THAT'S TOO LONG.
(Slam)
(Boom)
(Allelujah screaming)
(Screaming)
I SWEAR THIS...
I WILL COMPLETE THE
MISSION THIS TIME
AS A SUPER SOLDIER!
Hallelujah:
WHAT'S YOUR NAME?
A TRANSMISSION?
COME ON, TELL ME.
SUPER SOLDIER NUMBER ONE,
LIEUTENANT SOMA PERIES!
SOMA PERIES, HEY?
I LIKE THAT.
BUT I'LL LIKE KILLING YOU MORE!
(Gasps)
PULL BACK FOR NOW,
LIEUTENANT!
YES, COLONEL!
(Shots firing rapidly)
NAH...
THIS IS NO FUN.
I'LL LET YOU DEAL WITH
THE REST, ALLELUJAH.
HALLELUJAH!
(Screaming)
Alejandro:
FIVE HOURS HAVE PASSED
SINCE THE FIGHTING BEGAN.
WHERE ARE YOU GOING?
I'M GOING TO HEAR THE OPINIONS
OF THE OTHER OBSERVERS.
IT'S QUITE POSSIBLE MY
JOB COULD BE OVER HERE.
NO, THAT'S NOT WHAT
YOU'RE GOING TO DO.
I HATE ADULTS.
(Shots swarming)
Operator #15B:
SEVENTH MOBILE
SUIT TEAM
HAS REACHED ITS
OPERATING TIME LIMIT.
Kati:
HAVE THE SIXTEENTH MOBILE
SUIT TEAM TAKE OVER.
YOUR TURN'S COMING UP,
LIEUTENANT.
HURRY UP AND GET
READY TO LAUNCH.
MA'AM!
(Missiles whistling past)
(Explosions)
HOW MUCH LONGER
CAN THIS LAST?
THIS ATTACK
IS MURDER!
(Guns firing rapidly)
AT LEAST GIVE US
A BREAK TO EAT!
(Gasping)
(Growls)
THEY WILL NEVER
GET THESE GUNDAMS!
(Panting hard)
Sailor #15A:
OVER FLAGS SQUADRON,
MISSION TIME CLEARED.
ORDERS ACKNOWLEDGED.
THIS IS GRAHAM AKER,
LAUNCHING!
(Engine revving)
Patrick:
ATTENTION ALL UNITS!
OUR SQUADRON'S TARGET
IS THE GIANT GUNDAM.
WHEN THE BARRAGE STOPS,
THAT'S WHEN WE INITIATE
OUR CAPTURE PLAN!
WHATEVER YOU DO,
DON'T GET HIT BY ITS BEAMS.
(Boom)
(Sighs)
FIFTEEN HOURS SINCE
THE FIGHTING BEGAN...
(Groans)
(Panting)
(Force field humming)
WHAT THE...
IS THE ATTACK OVER?
WE'RE LEAVING!
ROGER THAT!
I'VE GOT YOU NOW GUNDAM!
(Growls)
(Blast)
Patrick:
WHAT'S THE MATTER?
YOU'RE A LITTLE
SLOW TODAY, GUNDAM!
Patrick:
DO IT!
(Electric buzzing)
(Screaming)
Pilot #15B:
GUNDAM IS SECURED!
Patrick:
GOOD WORK BOYS!
AND YOU COULDN'T HAVE
DONE IT WITHOUT ME!
Peries:
COLONEL, MOVING IN TO
CAPTURE THE WINGED ONE.
Sergei:
BE CAREFUL, LIEUTENANT.
IT COULD SUDDENLY
START MOVING AGAIN
LIKE IT DID LAST TIME.
ROGER, COLONEL.
COMMANDER. HAVE VISUAL OF
TARGET, COMMENCING OPERATION.
OVER FLAGS, WE'RE GOING TO START
THIS MISSION USING FORMATION E!
Daryl:
CAPTAIN!
IT'S JOSHUA!
(Growls)
JOSHUA!
DON'T BREAK FORMATION!
(Scoffs)
I'LL SHOW YOU HOW
A LEADER ACTS!
MID‐AIR TRANSFORMATION?
Joshua:
YOU LIKE THAT?
I BET YOU THOUGHT THAT WAS
YOUR OWN PERSONAL TRICK!
(Gasps)
NO!
(Boom)
Daryl:
JOSHUA'S GONE!
(Groans)
ALL RIGHT MEN, SWITCH
TO FORMATION C!
(Rapid blasting)
I'M STARTING TO LOSE
FEELING IN MY FINGERS.
TIME FOR A LOVER'S
EMBRACE, GUNDAM!
(Screaming)
Graham:
AND YOU ARE MY
SLEEPING BEAUTY!
Christina:
FELDT, HAVE YOU HEARD
ANYTHING FROM THE MEISTERS?
NOTHING YET.
WHAT THE HELL
IS GOING ON HERE?
THE LIVES OF THE
GUNDAM MEISTERS
MIGHT BE
COMING TO AN END.
HOW ARE THE OTHER
MEISTERS DOING?
(Beeping)
(Gasps)
ENEMY MACHINE AT
THREE O'CLOCK!
Setsuna:
A MOBILE ARMOR.
(Gasping)
IT'S THAT ENACT!
I'M GOING TO PAY YOU BACK
FOR THE LAST TIME!
READY, MISTER GUNDAM?
(Gasps)
(Rapid blasts)
(Crash)
YOU CAN DIE NOW.
(Electric buzzing)
(Screaming)
HOW DO YOU LIKE THE TASTE OF
THE AGRISSA'S PLASMA FIELD?
NOW, YOU'RE GOING TO DIE AND
LEAVE YOUR MACHINE BEHIND
YOU LITTLE KRUGIS PUNK!
(Screaming)
(Door opens)
THE FOREIGN AFFAIRS OFFICE JUST
RECEIVED AN UNOFFICIAL REPORT.
IT SEEMS THE GUNDAMS OF
CELESTIAL BEING
MADE AN APPEARANCE
AT THE JOINT MILITARY EXERCISE
NOW TAKING PLACE
IN EURASIA.
CELESTIAL BEING'S THERE?
THE TWO SIDES ARE ALREADY
FULLY ENGAGED IN COMBAT.
BUT TAKING ON NEARLY
A THOUSAND MOBILE SUITS
WITH ONLY FOUR GUNDAMS
IS JUST TOO RECKLESS,
EVEN FOR THEM.
YOUR HIGHNESS?
SETSUNA...
TELL ME... WHY IS THIS
WORLD SO TWISTED?
IS IT GOD'S FAULT?
OR IS IT OURS?
OH NO! WAS HE
TALKING ABOUT THIS?
(Screaming)
(Setsuna thinking):
AM I...
AM I GOING TO DIE?
IN THIS TWISTED WORLD
WITHOUT BECOMING ANYTHING?
AM I GOING TO ROT AWAY...
AFTER HAVING LOST EVERYTHING?
♪
GUN... DAM...
(Blast)
(Boom)
WHAT THE...
(Mechanical noises)
(Gasps)
IS THAT?
♪
WHAT THE HELL?
GUN... DAM...
(Struggling for breath)
Setsuna screaming:
GUNDAM!
♪
Narrator:
THE THRONES. THREE NEW GUNDAMS
MAKE THEIR ENTRANCE.
WHAT IS THE
SIGNIFICANCE
OF THE GN PARTICLES
THEY EMIT?
NEXT EPISODE:
"TRINITY".
THE TOLLING OF THE BELL
SIGNALS THE BEGINNING
OF THE SECOND ACT.