AS A RESULT OF CELESTIAL
BEING'S ARMED INTERVENTION
ON THE ISLAND OF CEYLON,
148 OF OUR BRAVE AND
NOBLE SOLDIERS
LOST THEIR LIVES.
ALTHOUGH THEY SPEAK OF
ELIMINATING CONFLICT,
CELESTIAL BEING'S ACTIONS
ARE NOTHING
MORE THAN TERRORISM,
PERPETRATED IN
A BLATANT ATTEMPT
TO DISRUPT
THE NATIONAL ORDER.
WE, THE PEOPLE OF THE HUMAN
REFORM LEAGUE,
INTEND TO TAKE A FIRM STANCE
AND CONFRONT
THEIR TERRORIST ACTIVITIES.
THEY SURE
DON'T LIKE US.
IT'S THE OBVIOUS
REACTION.
BUT ISN'T THE HUMAN REFORM
LEAGUE JUST GOING TO
BUILD UP ITS MILITARY IN
RESPONSE TO WHAT WE'RE DOING?
IF THAT'S WHAT
THEY SAY THEY'RE GOING TO DO
THEN WE'LL SIMPLY
HAVE TO RESPOND
WITH MORE
ARMED INTERVENTIONS.
THE ELIMINATION OF WAR.
YES. FOR THAT IS
CELESTIAL BEING'S
TRUE GOAL.
Chairman:
AND TO STOP CELESTIAL BEING
FROM PERPETRATING FURTHER
VIOLENCE,
THE UNION WILL
ALSO BE IMPLEMENTING NEW...
♪
Narrator:
2307 A. D. EARTH'S FOSSIL FUELS
HAVE BEEN DEPLETED.
THREE GROUPS OF NATIONS HAVE
CREATED ORBITAL ELEVATORS
AND A SOLAR
POWER GENERATION SYSTEM,
GIVING HUMANITY ACCESS
TO A NEARLY INFINITE
SOURCE OF ENERGY.
HOWEVER, TO FURTHER THEIR OWN
PRESTIGE AND PROSPERITY,
EACH GROUP OF NATIONS
INSISTS ON PLAYING
A GRAND ZERO‐SUM GAME.
YES, EVEN IN THE 24TH CENTURY,
HUMANITY IS STILL UNABLE
TO LIVE TOGETHER AS ONE.
BUT NOW A SMALL BAND OF
PEOPLE HAVE ARISEN
TO CHALLENGE THIS WORLD.
CELESTIAL BEING.
THE PRIVATE ARMED
ORGANIZATION
THAT POSSESSES THE MOBILE
SUITS CALLED...GUNDAMS.
IT HAS BEGUN CARRYING OUT
OPERATIONS THAT TRANSCEND RACE,
NATIONALITY AND RELIGION
IN A QUEST
TO ERADICATE WAR.
AND NOW ONCE AGAIN,
THE GUNDAM MEISTERS ARE
ABOUT TO BEGIN
A NEW MISSION THAT
HAS BEEN ASSIGNED THEM.
(Sirens wail)
(Boom)
WELL PRINCESS,
IT APPEARS THAT
THE WAVE OF TERRORISM
HAS FINALLY
REACHED THE CITY.
INDEED.
WE NEED TO PUSH
THE REFORMS THROUGH
BEFORE THE MODERATES DECIDE
TO JOIN THEM.
I AM AWARE OF THAT.
OUR COUNTRY HAS BEEN
RELIANT ON FOSSIL FUELS
FOR FAR TOO LONG.
TO REVIVE WE MUST
APPROACH THE NATIONS
THAT CONTROL
THE SOLAR POWER SYSTEM.
AND ASK FOR AID.
BUT SINCE OUR COUNTRY
DIDN'T PARTICIPATE
IN THE CONSTRUCTION
OF THE THREE
ORBITAL ELEVATORS,
WE DON'T HAVE
THE RIGHT TO
ACCESS
THEIR ENERGY SUPPLY.
NOW THAT OUR
PRECIOUS OIL IS SUBJECT
TO SEVERE EXPORT
RESTRICTIONS,
WHY WOULD ANY OTHER
NATION BE WILLING
TO HELP US FOR
NOTHING?
BUT THE NATIONAL ASSEMBLY
RESTORED THE MONARCHY
AND PUT ME IN POWER
TO FIND THAT ASSISTANCE.
THEREFORE, THERE'S ONLY
ONE TASK AHEAD OF ME.
STILL, THE IMMEDIATE
SITUATION IS DIRE.
IF THE COUNTRY DESCENDS
FURTHER INTO CHAOS,
THEY WILL COME.
THAT PRIVATE ARMED FORCE...
CALLED
CELESTIAL BEING.
(Gasps)
CELESTIAL BEING WILL COME...
(Bang)
(Sparking)
ALLELUJAH,
DID YOU HEAR?
THE REAL I. R. A.
DECLARED A CEASEFIRE.
YEAH.
THAT DECLARATION MIGHT
GET SOME COUNTRIES
TO LOOK AT US MORE
FAVORABLY.
BUT THAT'S NOT GOING
TO LAST FOR TOO LONG.
THEY ONLY
MADE THE FIRST MOVE
BECAUSE THEY'RE AFRAID
WE'D INTERVENE.
IF WE WEREN'T THERE TO KEEP
AN EYE ON THEM,
THEY'D JUST GO AHEAD
AND START UP ALL OVER AGAIN.
I KNOW THEY WOULD.
OUR GOAL IS
TO ELIMINATE WAR
AND THAT ISN'T GOING TO BE
AN EASY THING TO DO.
THAT'S WHY YOU SHOULD
HIT THE RACK
AND GET SOME REST
WHILE YOU CAN.
WE'LL BE
BUSY AGAIN REAL SOON.
REALIZING A PERMANENT PEACE...
THAT'S WHY THE
GUNDAMS WERE CREATED.
WELL, HOW WAS IT,
COLONEL?
YOU TRADED BLOWS
WITH THE GUNDAM, DIDN'T YOU?
I'D LIKE TO HEAR YOUR
HONEST OPINION
ON ITS CAPABILITIES.
I'LL DO MY BEST, SIR.
MY PERSONAL OPINION IS
I DON'T BELIEVE
THERE'S A MOBILE SUIT
IN THE ENTIRE WORLD
THAT CAN STAND UP
TO A GUNDAM
IN A FAIR FIGHT.
ITS PERFORMANCE
IS THAT OVERWHELMING?
THAT'S JUST MY OPINION, SIR.
THEN CALLING YOU DOWN HERE WAS
THE RIGHT THING TO DO.
COLONEL SMIRNOFF, YOU ARE
TO ACQUIRE A GUNDAM FOR US,
BEFORE THE UNION
OR THE A. E. U.
SIR!
I AM FORMING A TEAM
FOR THAT PURPOSE.
I'LL LEAVE THE SELECTION
OF PERSONNEL TO YOU.
BUT THERE IS ONE SOLDIER
I'D LIKE TO
ENTRUST YOU WITH.
PLEASE COME IN.
EXCUSE ME, SIR.
I AM LIEUTENANT SOMA PERIES,
SUPER SOLDIER NUMBER ONE.
DISPATCHED FROM THE
SUPER‐HUMAN INSTITUTE LABS.
SUPER‐HUMAN?
BUT SIR, I THOUGHT THAT
PROJECT WAS‐‐
APPARENTLY, THEY CONTINUED TO
CARRY IT OUT IN SECRET.
THE HIGHER UPS BELIEVE
IT MAY WELL BE OUR TRUMP CARD
AGAINST THE GUNDAMS.
AS OF TODAY,
I HAVE BEEN ASSIGNED
TO SERVE IN YOUR ELITE UNIT,
COLONEL.
IT IS A GREAT HONOR
TO MEET YOU, SIR.
YOU ARE MUCH
TOO YOUNG FOR THIS.
(Laughter)
BUT IT WAS
TOTALLY HILARIOUS!
YEAH, NO KIDDING!
ARE YOU BEING SERIOUS?
(Laughter continues)
(Boom)
(Screaming)
(Heavy breath echoes)
OH, YEAH!
NO WAY, REALLY?!
(Laughter)
HEY, IT'S YOU!
SAJI CROSSROAD.
THAT'S IT.
I CAN'T BELIEVE
YOU REMEMBERED MY NAME!
WHO IS THIS?
OH, HE LIVES
NEXT DOOR TO ME.
HE'S, UM...
SETSUNA F. SEIEI.
Eifman:
I'VE REINFORCED THE BACKPACK
AND THE JOINTS.
AND I'VE APPLIED
AN ANTI‐BEAM COATING
TO THE UNIT'S SURFACE.
FOR WEAPONRY I PROCURED
A NEW PROTOTYPE RIFLE
FROM THE IRIS CORPORATION.
IT'S MAGNIFICENT,
PROFESSOR.
BUT, EVEN WITH THE
ANTI‐G SYSTEM ACTIVATED,
YOU'LL BE FEELING
ABOUT 12GS
WHEN TURNING
AT FULL SPEED.
THAT'S EXACTLY WHAT
I WAS HOPING FOR.
SO! THIS IS
THE LIEUTENANT'S FLAG!
WARRANT OFFICER
HOWARD MASON,
MASTER SERGEANT
DARYL DODGE.
WE'VE BEEN ASSIGNED
TO THE ANTI‐GUNDAM
INVESTIGATIVE TASK FORCE
AS PER
YOUR REQUEST, SIR!
AH, YOU CAME.
LET ME WELCOME YOU,
FLAG FIGHTERS!
DID YOU SEE THE NEWS
THIS AFTERNOON, DAVID?
THE COMMENTATOR
WAS MAKING SUGGESTIONS
ABOUT APPOINTING
CELESTIAL BEING
AS A KIND OF WORLD POLICE
OR SOMETHING
ALONG THOSE LINES!
THAT'S A WONDERFUL IDEA.
AND UNLIKE THE UNITED NATIONS,
WE WOULDN'T HAVE TO PAY FOR IT!
(Scoffs)
MOST OF HUMANITY HAS
BLOOD ON ITS HANDS.
ALONG WITH ITS NATIONS.
I DOUBT ANYONE IS GOING TO BE
WILLING TO WORK WITH THEM.
(Knocking)
UH, MISTER PRESIDENT.
WE HAVE REPORTS THAT
TARIBIA IS GOING TO MAKE
AN ANNOUNCEMENT TOMORROW.
HMM...
Sumeragi:
VEDA, LET ME SEE
YOUR PREDICTION.
SO IT'S THE SAME AS MINE.
THERE ARE
TWELVE COUNTERPLANS.
NO MATTER WHICH ONE
WE CHOOSE,
THERE'S A GREAT DEAL OF RISK
ATTACHED TO EACH OF THEM.
WE KNOW WHAT HAS TO
BE DONE BUT IT'S SO HARD.
MISS SUMERAGI!
TARIBIA IS ON AIR MAKING
AN ANNOUNCEMENT RIGHT NOW!
I THOUGHT IT WOULD BE TARIBIA.
THE UNION IS A CONGRESS OF
OVER FIFTY COUNTRIES.
BUT IN FACT IT
FUNCTIONS AS A DICTATORSHIP
BY THE U. S.
WHICH CONTROLS THE DISTRIBUTION
OF SOLAR ENERGY...
DAVID, CALL A SPECIAL SESSION
OF THE UNION PARLIAMENT
AND ASSEMBLE THE REPRESENTATIVES
OF THE MAJOR NATIONS.
VERY WELL, SIR.
THEREFORE,
THE REPUBLIC OF TARIBIA
IS SECEDING FROM
THE UNION.
AND WE CLAIM INDEPENDENT
ACCESS TO THIS ENGERY!
IF ANY NATION BRINGS POLITICAL
OR MILITARY PRESSURE
TO BEAR IN
ORDER TO DENY US OUR CLAIM...
THEN WE SHALL RESPOND WITH
MILITARY ACTION!
OUR NATION
DEFIANTLY OPPOSES DOMINATION
BY THE DESPICABLE U. S.!
(Applause)
Shirin:
LOOKS LIKE TARIBIA'S
MAKING ITS MOVE.
THAT COUNTRY
HAS ALWAYS HAD
STRONG ANTI‐AMERICAN
SENTIMENTS.
BUT TO SECEDE FROM
THE UNION
AND DEMAND
THEIR ENERGY RIGHTS
LIKE THAT IS JUST‐‐
MAYBE IT'S POLITICAL
POSTURING
FOR THEIR
UPCOMING ELECTIONS.
NO WAY...
IF RELATIONS BETWEEN THE
COUNTRIES AROUND THE ELEVATOR
TAKE A TURN FOR
THE WORSE,
IT'LL ONLY INTERFERE
WITH THE OPERATION
OF THE SOLAR POWER SYSTEM.
OF COURSE,
AT THE REQUEST OF AMERICA,
THE UNION IS GOING TO BECOME
INVOLVED MILITARILY.
AND THAT IS
EXACTLY WHAT TARIBIA
IS PREDICTING WILL HAPPEN.
THEY KNOW IT.
LIEUTENANT, DO YOU KNOW
WHY TARIBIA
HAS DECIDED TO TAKE
SUCH A HARD‐LINE APPROACH?
IF THE UNION
TAKES MILITARY ACTION...
THEN THEY KNOW THAT
CELESTIAL BEING
WILL INTERVENE
IN ORDER TO PREVENT
A CONFLICT.
THAT'S IT EXACTLY.
WILL YOU ACCEPT THE INVITE,
GUNDAM, AND SHOW UP?
SO, YOU THINK TARIBIA IS TAKING
ADVANTAGE OF CELESTIAL BEING.
I'M JEALOUS OF THEM.
THE REASON THEY CAN TAKE
SUCH AN EXTORTIONIST,
HARD‐LINE APPROACH
IS BECAUSE OF THEIR PROXIMITY
TO THE ORBITAL ELEVATOR.
UNLIKE US,
THEY ACTUALLY HAVE
A CARD THEY CAN PLAY.
DO YOU THINK CELESTIAL BEING
WILL REALLY MAKE AN APPEARANCE?
WHO KNOWS?
BUT THE FUTURE
OF OUR OWN COUNTRY
MAY WELL
DEPEND ON HOW
CELESTIAL BEING DEALS
WITH TARIBIA.
THE FUTURE
OF OUR COUNTRY.
IT MEANS WE CAN TAKE
ADVANTAGE OF THEM, AS WELL.
(Sighs)
EVEN THOUGH WE KNOW
WE'RE BEING MANIPULATED,
WE'LL STILL MAKE
OUR MOVE.
BECAUSE THAT IS
WHAT CELESTIAL BEING DOES.
Everyone:
HMM?
PREPARE TO BEGIN
THE INTERVENTION.
CONTACT THE GUNDAM
MEISTERS IMMEDIATELY.
HAVING RECEIVED APPROVAL
FROM A MAJORITY OF
ITS PARLIAMENT,
THE UNION HAS MADE THE DECISION
TO DISPATCH A MILITARY FORCE
TO TARIBIA.
FURTHERMORE,
AMERICA HAS ANNOUNCED
THAT IT WILL BE SENDING AN
INDEPENDENT FORCE OF ITS OWN.
(Thinking)
TARIBIA...
HARO! LET'S GO!
ROGER! ROGER!
(Grunts)
(Splash)
♪
KYRIOS,
ALLELUJAH HAPTISM...
COMMENCING INTERVENTION.
DYNAMES, LOCKON STRATOS,
I'M GOING TO
SHOOT THEM UP!
EXIA, SETSUNA F. SEIEI,
HEADING OUT.
WE'RE FINALLY GOING
TO MEET THESE GUNDAMS.
I'M LOOKING FORWARD TO
THIS, LIEUTENANT!
YEAH, ME TOO!
LOOKING FORWARD TO SEEING HOW
THIS CUSTOM FLAG HERE
STANDS UP
AGAINST THE GUNDAMS.
BECAUSE, IT IS VITAL THAT
IT STANDS UP TO THEM!
Feldt:
THE UNION FLEET
AND AMERICA'S SECOND FLEET
HAVE ARRIVED OFF
THE COAST OF TARIBIA.
Christina:
AIR FORCES HAVE ALSO SCRAMBLED
FROM THE BRAZILIAN
GARRISON BASE.
IT LOOKS LIKE THEY
HAVE CONTROL OF THE AIRSPACE
OVER THE MAJOR TARIBIAN CITIES.
Sumeragi:
WHAT ABOUT THE TARIBIANS?
Christina:
THEY'RE CONCENTRATING
GROUND MOBILE SUITS
AROUND THREE
OF THEIR MAIN CITIES.
Lasse:
IT'S ABOUT WHAT
I EXPECTED.
SO WHAT ARE WE GOING TO BE
DOING, MISS SUMERAGI?
IT'S OBVIOUS.
THERE'S ONLY ONE THING
WE REALLY CAN DO.
UH...!
CAPTAIN!
A GUNDAM JUST SHOWED UP!
(Grunts)
SO THAT'S A GUNDAM!
Pilot:
THIS IS BLUE SHARK.
I HAVE A VISUAL ON
TWO GUNDAMS!
THEY'RE HEADING FOR
THE CAPITAL.
PREPARE TO INTERCEPT!
LOOKS LIKE COMMUNICATIONS
ARE BEING JAMMED.
THE GUNDAMS MUST BE
RESPONSIBLE.
MR. PRIME MINISTER,
CELESTIAL BEING
JUST APPEARED.
SO, THEY DID SHOW UP.
Sailor:
THE GUNDAMS HAVE SPLIT UP.
WE THINK EACH ONE IS
HEADING FOR A MAJOR CITY.
WHAT ARE THEY PLANNING?
ARE THEY
GOING TO INTERVENE
AGAINST BOTH AMERICA
AND THE UNION?!
IF CELESTIAL BEING
ACTUALLY INTERVENES,
IT'LL BE HELPING
THE HARD‐LINERS IN TARIBIA
WITH THEIR AGENDA.
BUT LET'S SAY
THEY DON'T INTERVENE.
IF THEY STAND BACK
AND ALLOW THE
UNION ARMED FORCES TO ATTACK,
THEIR DOCTRINE
OF ELIMINATING WAR
WILL BE HOPELESSLY COMPROMISED.
Newscaster:
IT IS EXPECTED THAT
CELESTIAL BEING WILL MAKE
AN ARMED INTERVENTION
IN THE SOUTH AMERICAN REGION.
THE QUESTION IS WHICH
ONE ARE YOU GOING TO CHOOSE,
CELESTIALBEING?
Newscaster:
HOW WILL CELESTIAL BEING MAKE
THEIR ARMED INTERVENTION?
COMMENCE MISSION.
(Shots firing)
WHAT THE...?
IS THIS THE START OF
THE UNION ATTACK?
(Beeping)
UH...
(Grunts)
A GUNDAM!
BUT... BUT WHY?!
WE HAVEN'T DONE ANYTHING
YET TO DESERVE THIS!
Liu‐Mei:
CELESTIAL BEING'S
FOUNDER WAS QUITE CLEAR.
AEOLIA SHENBERG EVEN
MENTIONED IT
DURING HIS
DECLARATION.
TO THE MEMBERS
OF CELESTIAL BEING,
ALL COUNTRIES THAT
PROMOTE WAR
ARE LEGITIMATE TARGETS FOR
ARMED INTERVENTION.
I'VE DETERMINED THAT
TARIBIA IS PROMOTING WAR.
ELIMINATING TARGETS.
(Shots firing)
(Clang)
KYRIOS, NOW COMMENCING
INTERVENTION MISSION.
(Firing continues)
DYNAMES, TARGETED AND
READY TO FIRE.
(Beeping)
TAKING ADVANTAGE OF US
WITHOUT OUR EXPRESS PERMISSION
IS NOT ALLOWED!
BUT THIS...
IT'S JUST SO ONE‐SIDED.
SIR, THE GUNDAMS ARE ENGAGING
THE TARIBIAN FORCES!
THEY'RE DOING WHAT?!
I SEE...
THE GUNDAMS ARE
ATTACKING OUR MILITARY.
GET ME PRESIDENT STEGMEYER
ON THE HOT LINE.
YES, SIR.
President:
IT SEEMS CELESTIAL BEING
HAS DETERMINED
THAT YOUR COUNTRY
IS A SOURCE OF CONFLICT.
CAUSING IT TO ATTACK YOU.
I SYMPATHIZE WITH
YOUR PLIGHT
AND I FEEL ITS
ACTIONS ARE REGRETTABLE.
OF COURSE,
IF YOU'RE WILLING TO REVERSE
YOUR DECISION TO SECEDE
FROM THE UNION,
WE WILL GLADLY
DEPLOY OUR ARMED FORCES
TO PROTECT YOUR COUNTRY.
I SEE. VERY WELL.
IN ORDER TO ENSURE
THE PROTECTION
OF THE REPUBLIC OF TARIBIA,
A NATION ALLIED
WITH US...
OUR MILITARY WILL LAUNCH
AN ATTACK ON
CELESTIAL BEING.
Christina:
THE AMERICAN MOBILE SUIT
TEAMS ARE TAKING OFF.
IT APPEARS THEY'RE ACTING TO
PROTECT TARIBIA, AS PREDICTED.
I SEE.
IN ACCORDANCE WITH
THE MISSION PLAN,
EACH GUNDAM WILL WITHDRAW
AND FALL BACK TO A SAFE ZONE.
WHAT A COMPLETE FARCE!
JUST A MOMENT!
I HAVE A MACHINE THAT
IS CURRENTLY
CLOSING IN ON THE EXIA!
IT'S ONE OF
AMERICA'S FLAGS!
AMERICAN?
WHAT ARE THEY UP TO?
IT'S MORE THAN
TWICE AS FAST AS ITS SPECS.
AND ITS HEADING
FOR THE EXIA!
IT'S THAT FLAG AGAIN.
ANOTHER CHANCE
TO FIGHT THE GUNDAM!
THAT, MR. PRESIDENT,
WAS WELL PLAYED!
(Gasps)
(Grunts)
(Shots firing)
HE'S FAST!
(Bang)
GOT HIM!
Howard:
EXCELLENT, LIEUTENANT!
Graham:
HE GOT AWAY.
IN THE CUSTOM FLAG...
I WAS ABLE TO STAND UP
TO THE GUNDAM.
BUT THEN IT TURNED OUT
TO HAVE UNDERWATER CAPABILITY.
YOU'RE JUST A LITTLE
TOO VERSATILE, GUNDAM.
I'M SHOCKED.
I NEVER EXPECTED THEM TO
ATTACK THE TARIBIANS.
IT LOOKS LIKE
BOTH TARIBIA AND AMERICA
EXPECTED SOMETHING
LIKE THIS WOULD HAPPEN.
THEY EXPECTED IT TO HAPPEN?
ONCE CELESTIAL BEING BEGAN
THEIR INTERVENTION,
TARIBIA IMMEDIATELY
BORROWED THE HELP
OF THE AMERICAN MILITARY.
(Gasps)
Shirin:
NOW, ANTI‐AMERICAN SENTIMENTS
WITHIN TARIBIA
WILL DIE DOWN AND AS A RESULT,
THEY CAN SUPPORT THE
U. S. LEADERSHIP
AS A MATTER OF POLICY.
THE CURRENT TARIBIAN
ADMINISTRATION
WILL HAVE AMERICAN AID AND
A MORE SECURE POWER BASE.
AND TO AVOID
TARIBIA'S FATE,
OTHER COUNTRIES WILL
THINK TWICE
BEFORE DECIDING TO IMPLEMENT
ANY OVERT
ANTI‐AMERICAN POLICIES.
(Sighs)
I JUST WONDER WHO
ACTUALLY BENEFITED
THE MOST
FROM THESE EVENTS?
IF YOU CAN'T UNDERSTAND THIS ...
THEN YOU'RE NOT QUALIFIED
TO SAVE THIS COUNTRY.
MARINA ISMAIL,
PRINCESS ROYAL OF
THE KINGDOM OF AZADISTAN.
HEY, SIS, WHAT DOES
ALL THIS MEAN, ANYWAY?
CELESTIAL BEING ATTACKED
THE TARIBIAN ARMY.
BUT THAT COUNTRY DIDN'T EVEN
START A FIGHT OR ANYTHING.
YOU'RE RIGHT.
THEY SAID THEY WERE GOING
TO END FIGHTING AND WAR...
BUT THEY STARTED
THIS ONE.
THAT JUST DOESN'T
SEEM RIGHT!
I HATE TO
TELL YOU SAJI,
BUT SOMETIMES THE WORLD
JUST ISN'T THAT SIMPLE.
NO, THE WORLD ISN'T
SIMPLE AT ALL.
♪
Narrator:
AN ENCOUNTER
ON A LOW ORBITAL STATION
DRAWS ALLELUJAH INTO THE PAST.
HURRY, KYRIOS, BEFORE LIVES
ARE LOST AND FADE AWAY.
NEXT EPISODE,
"ESCAPE LIMIT ZONE".
IRRESISTIBLE GRAVITY
EATS AWAY AT THE GUNDAM.