(Rain falling)
HMM?
BUT WHO WOULD HAVE...
COULD THIS BE...FROM HIM?
♪
Narrator:
2307 A. D.
ALMOST FOUR
MONTHS HAVE PASSED
SINCE CELESTIAL BEING
COMMENCED
ITS ARMED INTERVENTIONS.
IN THAT TIME, IT HAS
CARRIED OUT
OVER SIXTY OF
THESE INTERVENTIONS.
REGARDLESS OF WHETHER IT IS
LOVED OR HATED,
WHAT MATTERS
IS THAT PEOPLE
HAVE HAD TO
ACKNOWLEDGE ITS EXISTENCE.
THERE WERE THOSE WHO WOULD
REBUKE CELESTIAL BEING,
AND THOSE WHO
WOULD AFFIRM IT...
BUT WHEN IT COMES TO
REJECTING WAR
BOTH SIDES FIND THEMSELVES
IN COMPLETE AGREEMENT.
NO ONE SEEKS CONFLICT
FOR ITS OWN SAKE.
OF THE THREE GROUPS
OF NATIONS ON EARTH,
THE UNION AND THE AEU
HAVE ANNOUNCED
THAT THEY WILL
ONLY TAKE DEFENSIVE MEASURES
AGAINST CELESTIAL BEING
IN CONFLICTS
THAT OCCUR WITHIN
THEIR TERRITORIES.
HOWEVER, SINCE THE CONFLICT
IN MORALIA...
THERE HASN'T BEEN
A SINGLE LARGE SCALE BATTLE.
THIS STATE OF AFFAIRS HAS
BEEN BROUGHT ABOUT
BECAUSE OF
THE SUPERIOR COMBAT ABILITIES
OF THE GUNDAM MOBILE SUITS.
ALTHOUGH THE INCIDENTS OF
BLOODSHED
AROUND THE WORLD
CONTINUE TO DIMINISH,
RESISTANCE AGAINST OPPRESSION
BY ARMED FORCE
HAS NOT DISAPPEARED.
AND NOW A SECRET PLAN IS BEING
SET IN MOTION
BY THE ONLY GROUP
TO CHALLENGE CELESTIAL BEING...
THE HUMAN REFORM LEAGUE.
Sergei:
MEMBERS OF THE CHOBU SPECIAL
FORCES TEAM:
YOU REPRESENT YOUR
MOTHERLANDS AND ARE
THE FINEST THAT THE HUMAN
REFORM LEAGUE HAS TO OFFER.
YOUR MISSION IS
TO ENGAGE AND DESTROY
THAT ARMED GROUP OF
GLOBAL INTERVENTIONISTS...
AND SEIZE THEIR MOBILE
SUITS AS YOU DO SO.
THE SUCCESSFUL
COMPLETION OF THIS MISSION
WILL MAKE THE HUMAN
REFORM LEAGUE
THE LEADER OF THE
WORLD THEREBY CONTRIBUTING
TO THE OVERALL ADVANCEMENT
OF HUMANITY!
I EXPECT GREAT
THINGS FROM YOU ALL!
Christina:
DYNAMES,
DOCKING COMPLETE.
CONTINUE WITH EXIA
DOCKING PROCEDURE.
Feldt:
CONTAINER OPEN. RELATIVE
GUIDANCE SYSTEM ACTIVATED.
Setsuna:
GUIDANCE SYSTEM LOCKED IN.
EXIA, NOW DOCKING.
Christina:
EXIA HAS DOCKED.
(Hatch slams shut)
THAT WAS A PRETTY
GOOD LANDING, SETSUNA.
I'LL HELP YOU
WITH MAINTENANCE.
GO BACK TO YOUR ROOM
AND GET SOME REST.
GIVE OTHER PEOPLE A
CHANCE TO DO SOME WORK.
BROTHER!
HEY BRO HEY BRO! BIG BROTHER! WHAT'S NEW
NOW THAT'S A
WELCOMING COMMITTEE!
BEGIN MAINTENANCE!
ROGER! ROGER!
ROGER! ROGER! ROGER! ROGER!
PLAY NICE NOW KIDS!
Allelujah:
MISS SUMERAGI...
WHAT IF WE COME UNDER
ATTACK DURING OUR OVERHAUL?
THEN I'LL CURSE GOD FOR THAT.
I DON'T KNOW IF
A TACTICAL FORECASTER
SHOULD BE SAYING THAT.
♪
(Door slides open)
Operator #9A:
ATTITUDE CONTROL COMPLETE.
HATCHES OPEN.
Operator #9B:
INCREASING LINEAR
CATAPULT VOLTAGE.
TWO‐WAY COMMUNICATION
SYSTEM READY FOR LAUNCH.
Operator #9A:
LAUNCHING.
Operator #9B:
FULL DEPLOYMENT OF PROBES.
Operator #9A:
ALL PROBES NOW
FULLY DEPLOYED.
MOVING TO DESIGNATED POSITIONS.
Operator #9:
TWO‐WAY COM‐LINKS
ARE OPERATIONAL.
WE HAVE NOW COVERED
APPROXIMATELY EIGHTY PERCENT
OF OUR FORCES' TERRITORY
IN GEOSTATIONARY
SATELLITE ORBIT.
HMM.
THE SPECIAL PARTICLES THAT THE
GUNDAMS EMIT
DISRUPT ALL
COMMUNICATION DEVICES
THAT COME
WITHIN THE AREA OF EFFECT.
WE'RE TAKING ADVANTAGE
OF THAT
BY RELEASING SEVERAL
HUNDRED THOUSAND SMALL PROBES
WITH TWO‐WAY COMM ABILITY.
IF COMMUNICATIONS FAIL
IN A GIVEN AREA,
THEN THAT MEANS THERE'S
A GUNDAM IN THE VICINITY.
SO COLONEL,
DO YOU REALLY THINK
THAT WE'RE GOING TO CATCH
ANY FISH IN THIS NET?
WE HAVE A PROBLEM IF WE
CAN'T, LIEUTENANT MING.
WE DON'T HAVE THE RESOURCES
TO MOUNT AN OPERATION
OF THIS SIZE VERY OFTEN.
Saji:
"CELESTIAL BEING'S INFLUENCE ON
THE FUTURE OF GLOBAL CONFLICT."
THIS IS GOING TO BE A
PRETTY TOUGH PAPER...
THEN WHY DON'T YOU
JUST MAKE SOMETHING UP?
YOU KNOW
I CAN'T DO THAT.
LOUISE!
Louise:
MOM?
(Laughing)
LOUISE,
I'VE MISSED YOU SO MUCH!
THERE ARE ALL SORTS OF TRAVEL
RESTRICTIONS RIGHT NOW,
HOW DID YOU
MANAGE TO GET HERE?
I JUST USED MY CONNECTIONS
AND ASKED FOR HELP.
LOUISE...
WHO IS THIS?
I TOLD YOU ABOUT HIM.
THIS IS MY BOYFRIEND, MOM.
MY NAME'S SAJI.
SAJI CROSSROAD, MA'AM.
ARE YOU? WELL, THANK YOU
FOR TAKING CARE OF
MY DAUGHTER.
YOU'RE WELCOME.
BUT, YOU DON'T
HAVE TO ANYMORE.
WE'RE GOING HOME NOW,
YOUNG LADY.
WHAT ARE YOU
TALKING ABOUT, MOM?
WITH THE CONDITION THE
WORLD IS IN RIGHT NOW,
I CAN'T LET MY ONLY DAUGHTER
STUDY ABROAD. COME.
NO! I'M NOT GOING!
SAJI, COME ON,
SAY SOMETHING!
UM, WHAT SHOULD I SAY?
YOUR LOVER IS BEING
TAKEN AWAY FROM YOU!
HER LOVER?
HEY, WHEN DID THAT HAPPEN?!
WHY YOU LITTLE‐‐
IT'S A MISUNDERSTANDING, "MOM"!
DID YOU SAY MOM?
NO! I DIDN'T MEAN IT
LIKE THAT! UH...
ACT LIKE A MAN AND
STAND UP TO HER, SAJI!
WHAT?
SAJI!
(Sighs)
Journalist #3A:
AN INVESTIGATIVE REPORT
ON AEOLIA SCHENBERG?
I FEEL THAT IF WE
INVESTIGATE
CELESTIAL BEING'S
FOUNDER WE MIGHT JUST DISCOVER
WHAT ITS TRUE OBJECTIVES ARE.
PLEASE, LET ME DO THIS, BOSS!
I HEARD THAT ALL THE NATIONAL
INTELLIGENCE AGENCIES
JUST GAVE UP ON IT.
WHAT CAN YOU DO
ON YOUR OWN?
AT LEAST LET ME
TRY IT!
COME ON,
CHIEF! PLEASE!
(Sighs)
THINK YOU CAN PULL TOGETHER
ENOUGH MATERIAL
FOR A ONE HOUR
SPECIAL REPORT IN A MONTH?
YEAH, YOU BET!
NOW, OUR NEXT ITEM...
IT SEEMS THE UNITED NATIONS
WILL BE ASSISTING
THE MIDDLE EASTERN
KINGDOM OF AZADISTAN,
WHICH IS CURRENTLY SUFFERING A
SEVERE ENERGY CRISIS.
A U. N. INSPECTION TEAM HAS
ARRIVED IN THE COUNTRY
AND IS PREPARING
TO CONDUCT A TOUR.
(Thinking):
IF TALKS GO WELL WITH THE
U. N. AMBASSADOR,
WE COULD FINALLY GAIN ACCESS
TO THE SOLAR POWER SYSTEM.
THE AMBASSADOR IS
ARRIVING NOW, PRINCESS.
(Cameras clicking)
(Marina thinking):
THIS IS THE PERSON WHO
COULD SAVE AZADISTAN.
IT IS A GREAT
PLEASURE TO MEET YOU.
I AM U. N. AMBASSADOR,
ALEJANDRO CORNER.
I AM MARINA ISMAIL,
PRINCESS ROYAL OF THE
KINGDOM OF AZADISTAN.
ON BEHALF OF MY NATION, I WANT
TO THANK YOU FOR ACCEPTING
OUR REQUEST FOR ASSISTANCE
IN OUR TIME OF NEED.
THE U. N. WAS ORIGINALLY
MEANT
FOR EXACTLY
THIS KIND OF PURPOSE.
THOUGH, BECAUSE MEMBER
NATIONS ARE LESS GENEROUS
WITH THEIR FUNDING THESE DAYS,
THERE IS A LIMIT
AS TO WHAT WE CAN
ACTUALLY ACCOMPLISH.
NEVERTHELESS,
WE ARE VERY GRATEFUL.
(Thinking):
WHY ARE WE RECEIVING U. N.
ASSISTANCE NOW,
WHEN WE HAVE
NOTHING TO OFFER IN RETURN?
WHAT IS THAT MAN
REALLY UP TO?
(Door slides open)
HEY, WHERE'S FELDT?
SHE SAID SHE WASN'T
FEELING WELL
AND WENT TO SEE DR. MORENO.
SO YOU'RE WORKING
A DOUBLE SHIFT?
YEAH, YOU GOT THAT RIGHT.
HEY, I'LL TAKE OVER
FOR A WHILE,
WHY DON'T YOU
GO GET SOMETHING TO EAT?
WHAT? REALLY?
THAT'S SO NICE!
AH, DON'T MENTION IT.
IT'S JUST TOO BAD
YOU'RE NOT REALLY MY TYPE!
YEAH, TOO BAD.
YO! WHAT'RE YOU UP TO?
LOCKON...
WHAT'S THE MATTER?
(Sighs)
(Eating quietly)
(Christina thinking):
THIS IS SO AWKWARD!
GN DRIVE CHARGING.
IT IS NOW READING
ONE HUNDRED PERCENT!
(Beeping)
Operator #9A:
WE'VE JUST LOST TWO‐WAY
COMMUNICATION WITH AE3288!
Ming:
NOTIFY THE COLONEL
IMMEDIATELY!
Operator #9B:
AND AR9763! LOCATION: N‐07.
I NEVER EXPECTED
THEM TO BE SO CLOSE.
ALRIGHT, NOTIFY THE CHOBU
SPECIAL FORCES TEAM!
MOBILE SUIT TEAMS:
SCRAMBLE IMMEDIATELY!
Ming:
PREPARE FOR IMMEDIATE
DEPLOYMENT!
LAUNCH IN SEQUENCE
FROM SHIP ONE AT 0655!
Ming:
ALL CREW MEMBERS,
PREPARE FOR ACCELERATION!
EMERGENCY ACCELERATION
IN 140 SECONDS!
LIEUTENANT PERIES...
HOW'S THE FULL SENSORY
PROJECTION SYSTEM?
NO PROBLEM, COLONEL SMIRNOV.
EVERYTHING IS GREEN
ACROSS THE BOARD.
Sergei:
THIS WILL BE YOUR FIRST
REAL BATTLE, LIEUTENANT.
I WANT TO AVOID A REPEAT
OF WHAT HAPPENED BEFORE.
YOU'VE GOT NOTHING
TO WORRY ABOUT, SIR.
Ming:
ALL SHIPS HAVE REACHED
THE ACCELERATION ZONE.
COMMENCING ACCELERATION!
REALLY...
SO BOTH YOUR PARENTS
WERE MEMBERS OF
CELESTIAL BEING AS WELL?
YEAH, THEY WERE BOTH SECOND
GENERATION GUNDAM MEISTERS.
I SEE.
THEN I GUESS I'M
ABLE TO FIGHT
THANKS TO THE
WORK YOUR PARENTS DID.
SO, DID YOU GET HOMESICK
OR SOMETHING FELDT?
IT'S THE ANNIVERSARY...
OF THEIR DEATHS.
OH, WHAT HAPPENED?
I DON'T REALLY KNOW.
I ONLY KNOW THEY DIED.
ALL THE MEMBERS OF
CELESTIAL BEING
ARE SWORN TO SECRECY.
I DON'T KNOW
A SINGLE THING
ABOUT ANY OF THE
CURRENT MEMBERS.
BUT STILL...
NOT TELLING YOU
ABOUT YOUR PARENTS...
YOU'RE FOLLOWING
IN THEIR FOOTSTEPS.
YOU'RE STRONG, FELDT...
YOU'RE A REMARKABLY
STRONG GIRL.
IT'S NEIL.
HUH?
THAT'S MY REAL NAME.
NEIL DYLANDY.
YOUR REAL NAME?
YEAH, THAT'S RIGHT, FELDT.
I'M FROM IRELAND ORIGINALLY.
MY PARENTS WERE
KILLED BY TERRORISTS.
WHY TELL ME THAT?
I THOUGHT
IT WOULD BE UNFAIR
IF YOU WERE THE ONLY ONE
SHARING YOUR PAST.
YOU'RE SO KIND.
YEAH, BUT ONLY TO THE LADIES.
LOCKON.
SORRY.
HEY, IT'S NOT LIKE THAT!
PHEW!
I COULDN'T EVEN TASTE MY FOOD,
IT WAS SO TENSE IN THERE!
YOU WHAT?
OH, NOTHING...
HUH?
SOMETHING ON THE E‐SENSOR...
THOSE ARE COMM DEVICES!
WHAT'S THE MATTER?
IDIOT!
WHAT DID I DO?
THE ENEMY KNOWS
OUR EXACT LOCATION!
Sumeragi:
ADJUST PTOLEMY'S COURSE.
PLOT THE SHORTEST ROUTE
TO THE ORBITAL RING.
Lichtendahl:
ROGER.
Sumeragi:
ALL MEISTERS, STAND
BY YOUR GUNDAMS.
IAN, WHAT'S THEIR
MAINTENANCE STATUS?
EXIA'S ALL FINISHED .
BUT DYNAMES CAN'T
USE ITS LEG GENERATORS...
AND ITS ARMOR IS STILL
STRIPPED.
THAT'S THE ONE I WANTED...
Sumeragi:
SEND OUT KYRIOS
AND VIRTUE FIRST.
RIGHT AWAY!
WAIT, FELDT...
MAKE SURE YOU SURVIVE.
Christina:
PTOLEMY: SWITCHING
TO CATAPULT MODE.
THEY SCATTERED HUNDREDS OF
THOUSANDS
OF COMM DEVICES
TO FIND THE AREAS WHERE
GN PARTICLES INTERFERE WITH
COMMUNICATIONS.
THE ONLY GROUP WITH THE
RESOURCES
TO MOUNT THIS
KIND OF OPERATION
IS THE HUMAN REFORM LEAGUE.
Sumeragi:
WHAT'S THE SITUATION?
NOT GOOD. WE CAN'T GET OUT OF
ENEMY COMMUNICATION RANGE.
WE NEED TO HEAD FOR THE ORBITAL
RING'S POWER SATELLITES.
THE ELECTROMAGNETIC FIELD MAKES
IT A COMMUNICATION DEAD ZONE.
WE'LL BE ABLE TO ERASE
OUR HANDICAP THERE.
RIGHT, CONSIDER IT DONE.
Christina:
KYRIOS HAS JUST LAUNCHED.
MOVING VIRTUE TO
THE CATAPULT DECK.
SO, YOU'RE GOING TO DRAW THEM
OFF WITH THE TWO GUNDAMS?
YEAH, THAT'S PART OF IT.
SORRY I'M LATE.
Christina:
FELDT, TAKE CARE OF
THE LAUNCHES, PLEASE.
ROGER.
Ian: I DID A QUICK FIX BY
PUTTING A STABILIZER ON THE LEFT
LEG,
BUT THE FIRE
CONTROL TUNING IS STILL‐‐
AS LONG AS I CAN SHOOT!
GO GET 'EM!
GO GET 'EM GO GET 'EM! GO GET 'EM! GO GET 'EM! GO GET 'EM GO GET 'EM!
THIS IS VIRTUE, TIERIA
ERDE... LAUNCHING.
Ming:
COLONEL, WE HAVE TWO ADDITIONAL
COMMUNICATION CUTOFF POINTS
AND THEY'RE
HEADED FOR THE RINGS.
ARE THE GUNDAMS
SPLITTING THEIR FORCES?
NO, THEY'RE TRYING TO
DRAW US OFF
BY SENDING OUT JUST TWO.
THEN THAT MEANS,
THERE'S A HIGH PROBABILITY
THAT THE FIRST CUTOFF POINT
IS ACTUALLY
CELESTIAL BEING'S
SPACE TRANSPORT.
THEN LET'S FALL FOR IT
AND THROW OUR OWN FEINT
RIGHT BACK AT THEM.
Sergei:
SHIPS ONE, TWO, AND THREE,
LAUNCH ALL MOBILE SUITS.
NAVIGATORS ON TWO AND THREE,
SWITCH TO AUTO‐PILOT,
DETACH BRIDGE
AND RETURN TO BASE.
NUMBER THREE, DON'T FORGET
YOU'RE TRACKING
THE THIRD
COMMUNICATION CUTOFF POINT.
Pilot #9A:
SHIPS ONE, TWO, AND THREE
LAUNCHING ALL MOBILE SUITS.
ASSUMING
STRAIGHT LINE FORMATION
BEHIND SHIP NUMBER ONE
AS PLANNED.
Pilot #9B:
SHIPS TWO AND THREE
DETACHING BRIDGES.
SHIP THREE TRACKING THIRD
COMMUNICATION CUTOFF POINT.
SHIP TWO, CHANGING COURSE
AND TRACKING SECOND
COMMUNICATION CUTOFF POINT.
SHIP ONE WILL LEAD OUR
MAIN FORCE
STRAIGHT BACK TO THE FIRST
COMMUNICATION CUTOFF POINT.
OUR TARGET IS THE POSSIBLE
ENEMY CARRIER.
WHEN YOU CATCH IT,
COMMENCE OPERATIONAL MANEUVERS!
Christina:
PTOLEMY HAS ENTERED THE
ORBITAL RING'S
ELECTROMAGNETIC
INTERFERENCE ZONE.
Feldt:
WE'RE GETTING A VISUAL
OF THE ENEMY FORCES
THEY'RE HERE.
Christina:
BRINGING UP MAXIMUM
MAGNIFICATION.
THE APPROACHING SHIPS ARE
FOUR HUMAN REFORM LEAGUE
MULTIPURPOSE TRANSPORTS
DESIGNATED EDI‐402 LAOHO.
TWO SHIPS ARE
BREAKING OFF,
TO THE LEFT
AND TO THE RIGHT.
PROBABLY TO ENGAGE
KYRIOS AND VIRTUE.
THEY FIGURED IT OUT.
CONTACT ALLELUJAH AND TIERIA.
BUT WE'RE IN THE INTERFERENCE
ZONE! IT'S IMPOSSIBLE!
LICHTY, CHANGE
COURSE IMMEDIATELY!
I NEED YOU TO GET AWAY FROM
THE ENEMY SHIPS
AND USE THE
ORBITAL RING AS A SHIELD!
ROGER THAT!
Ming:
ENEMY SHIP IS CHANGING COURSE.
IT'S HIDING BEHIND THE RING.
THEY'RE SHOWING SOME SKILL.
CAN WE GET A SILHOUETTE
OF THEIR SHIP?
Ming:
IT'LL BE AN A. I.
INTERPRETATION, SIR.
THAT'S FINE. GET IT.
SO THIS IS CELESTIAL
BEING'S SPACESHIP.
HOW LARGE MUST THAT
ORGANIZATION BE
IN ORDER TO
POSSESS SOMETHING LIKE THAT?
I'M GOING TO RELAY MY
TACTICAL FORECAST
OF THE SITUATION
TO ALL PERSONNEL.
I EXPECT THE SHIPS
APPROACHING US
WILL BE TWO LAOHO TRANSPORTS.
THOSE TWO SHIPS SHOULD HAVE
ALL OF THE ENEMY'S
FIGHTING STRENGTH.
ARE YOU SURE ABOUT THAT?
Lasse:
WE KNOW THAT TWO SHIPS
ARE MOVING
TO ENGAGE
KYRIOS AND VIRTUE.
YEAH, I WAS KIND OF HOPING
THEY WOULDN'T DO THAT.
MY ORIGINAL PLAN HAD THE ENEMY
FLEET SEEING THROUGH MY FEINT,
IGNORING ALLELUJAH AND TIERIA,
AND COMING STRAIGHT AT OUR SHIP.
THEN, THE TWO GUNDAMS WOULD HAVE
BEEN ABLE
TO MAKE A
PINCER ATTACK FROM BEHIND.
BUT THE ENEMY RESPONDED TO OUR
FEINT. WITH ONE OF THEIR OWN.
I'M AFRAID THE MOBILE SUITS ON
THOSE TWO ATTACKING SHIPS
HAVE ALREADY BEEN LAUNCHED
AND ALLELUJAH AND TIERIA
ARE NOW WASTING TIME
INTERCEPTING EMPTY ENEMY
TRANSPORTS.
(Boom)
WELL, THAT WAS
A WASTE OF TIME.
Allelujah:
THEY WEREN'T CARRYING
ANY MOBILE SUITS.
THAT MEANS...
MY FORECAST HAS THEM
TAKING SIX MINUTES
TO GET BACK TO US AFTER
DEALING WITH THE ENEMY'S FEINT.
IN THE MEANTIME, WE'RE
GOING TO BE ATTACKED
BY WAVES
OF ENEMY MOBILE SUITS.
MISS SUMERAGI, WHAT EXACTLY
ARE YOU BASING THIS ON?
I'M FAIRLY CERTAIN THE
EXACT SAME TACTIC WAS USED
EIGHTEEN YEARS AGO DURING
THE FOURTH SOLAR POWER WAR.
THE HUMAN REFORM LEAGUE'S
OPERATION COMMANDER WAS
CALLED "THE WILD BEAR OF
RUSSIA". SERGEI SMIRNOV.
MAIN FORCE, LET'S
BEGIN THE OPERATION!
DON'T THROW YOUR
LIVES AWAY TODAY!
Feldt:
EXIA, DYNAMES... OPENING
CONTAINER HATCHES.
Feldt:
EXIA IS TO TAKE UP AN
INTERCEPTION POSITION
IN FRONT OF THE PTOLEMAIOS.
Feldt:
DYNAMES IS TO SECURE ITS LEGS
TO THE CONTAINER
AND STANDBY TO
INTERCEPT WITH ITS GN RIFLE .
PTOLEMY'S PRIORITIES HAVE
NOW BEEN SHIFTED TO DEFENSE.
DISENGAGING NORMAL POWER.
WAIT, ARE WE REALLY
GOING TO FIGHT THOSE GUYS?
BUT THIS
SHIP'S UNARMED!
YEAH, BUT WE'VE GOT GUNDAMS!
ONLY TWO
OF THEM...
THE ENEMY SHOULD BE SHOWING UP RIGHT ABOUT NOW!
THE ENEMY SHOULD BE
SHOWING UP RIGHT ABOUT NOW.
TRY TO LAST FOR 360 SECONDS.
Feldt:
ENEMY TRANSPORT EMERGING
FROM BEHIND RING!
DYNAMES, OPEN FIRE!
Lockon:
I'M ON IT!
MY AIM IS OFF BECAUSE THE
MACHINE'S WEIGHT IS DIFFERENT!
HARO ADJUSTING! HARO ADJUSTING!
THERE'S NO TIME.
I'M JUST GOING TO WING IT.
WE HAVE INCOMING MISSILES.
TWENTY‐FOUR OF THEM!
Lockon:
I'M TAKING THEM OUT!
(Guns blasting)
DAMMIT!
DEPLOY GN FIELD!
ROGER THAT, MA'AM!
(Boom)
IT'S TOO FAST!
THEY'RE RAMMING US
WITH AN UNMANNED SHIP!
THEY'RE GOING TO RAM?
NO! NO!
NO, YOU DON'T!
♪
(Sparks flying)
(Boom)
REDEPLOY GN FIELD!
NO... NO...
COME ON, CHRIS‐‐
(Boom)
PLEASE HURRY BACK,
ALLELUJAH.
I DON'T WANT TO DIE,
I DON'T WANT TO DIE...
CHRISTINA SIERRA!
WE'RE GOING TO SURVIVE!
(Siren wailing)
WE'RE ALL...
GOING TO SURVIVE.
FELDT.
YEAH, IT'S JUST LIKE
FELDT SAID.
WE'RE GOING TO SURVIVE THIS!
WE'RE GOING TO GET THROUGH
THIS NO MATTER WHAT!
Lockon:
I'M CONFIRMING ENEMY
MOBILE SUIT TEAMS.
HUH?
LOOKS LIKE THEY WERE HIDING
BEHIND THEIR LITTLE TRANSPORTS.
I'M COUNTING
THIRTY‐SIX ENEMY UNITS.
SO YOU THINK YOU'RE
CLEVER, DO YOU?!
THEY'RE IN MY BLIND SPOT!
BRIDGE, TURN THE
CONTAINER RIGHT NOW!
(Guns blasting)
THEY WANT ME TO FOLLOW.
IF I GO OUT TOO FAR,
OUR DEFENSES WILL COLLAPSE.
Lockon:
GOT YOU!
NOT AGAIN!
Lasse:
THE ENEMY IS GETTING COLD FEET.
Lichtendahl:
YEAH, AND THE GN FIELD CAN
TAKE THIS KIND OF ATTACK.
HANG ON CHRISTINA...
I HEAR YOU, FELDT.
JUST A LITTLE...
LITTLE LONGER.
THIS LONG‐RANGE ATTACK GOES
AGAINST STANDARD DOCTRINE
FOR A MOBILE
SUIT ASSAULT ON A SHIP...
I GET IT!
THAT'S WHAT THIS IS!
THE HRL...NO.
ACTUALLY IT MUST BE SERGEI
SMIRNOV. HIS OBJECTIVE
ISN'T THE PTOLEMY,
HE WANTS TO CAPTURE A GUNDAM!
(Slam)
MY FORECASTING WAS
COMPLETELY OFF!
DAMN IT ALL...
I SWORE I WOULD NEVER
MAKE ANOTHER MISTAKE!
I CAN SEE THEM.
WHAT'S ALL THIS?
(Gasps)
A MINEFIELD! THEY LURED ME IN!
THAT WAS NOTHING TO KYRIOS‐‐
(Zap)
(Gasps in pain)
WHY IS MY HEAD FILLED WITH
THIS SHARP STABBING PAIN?
I'VE FELT THIS BEFORE.
(Gasps)
IT'S THE SAME PAIN!
WHAT...IS IT?
WHAT COULD IT BE?
(Gasps)
THAT MACHINE...
I KNOW YOU.
I KNOW YOU!
♪
Narrator:
CELESTIAL BEING HAS BEEN
CAUGHT IN A TRAP.
KYRIOS IS URGED TO
AWAKEN AMIDST THIS,
AND VIRTUE REVEALS
ITS HIDDEN ABILITIES.
NEXT EPISODE,
"OPERATION: GUNDAM CAPTURE".
AN ANGEL'S WINGS
SOAR THROUGH SPACE.