ACCORDING TO
THE JNN RESEARCH TEAM,
IT APPEARS THAT OVER THE COURSE
OF THE PAST TWO HUNDRED YEARS,
MANY SCIENTISTS AND ENGINEERS
HAVE VANISHED
UNDER MYSTERIOUS
CIRCUMSTANCES.
WE CAN SAFELY ASSUME THAT
CELESTIAL BEING IS SOMEHOW
INVOLVED IN THAT.
DEVELOPING AN ENTIRELY
NEW MOBILE SUIT
TAKES A MINIMUM OF 10 YEARS!
SO YOU'RE SAYING
THEY SET THIS PLAN IN MOTION
OVER TWO HUNDRED YEARS AGO?
THEY DIDN'T HAVE
TO DO THIS.
BUT IT'S STILL
MOSTLY CONJECTURE.
THE CIVILIAN MEDIA CAN'T
POSSIBLY GO DEEPER
THAN WHAT THEY'VE
FOUND SO FAR.
HMM?
VERY WELL, THEN.
IT'S BEEN AWHILE SINCE
I'VE SEEN YOU TWO.
I BELIEVE
THE LAST TIME WE MET
WAS THE SOLAR POWER
GENERATION SUMMIT.
IT'S A SHAME ABOUT THAT SCANDAL
WITH THE SUPER HUMAN INSTITUTE.
I DID NOT COME HERE
TO ENGAGE IN IDLE GOSSIP.
THIS IS AN UNOFFICIAL
MEETING.
LET US GET TO
THE MATTER AT HAND.
I'VE GONE OVER THE MATERIALS
THOROUGHLY.
IF THIS PROPOSAL
BECOMES A REALITY,
IT WOULD MARK THE WORLD'S
FIRST ATTEMPT.
I BELIEVE THE REWARD
IS MORE THAN WORTH THE EFFORT
IF WE GET A HOLD OF THE GUNDAMS.
♪
Narrator:
LAGRANGE ONE.
THE BALANCE POINT OF GRAVITY
AND CENTRIFUGAL FORCE
THAT LIES BETWEEN
THE EARTH AND THE MOON.
THIS IS THE LOCATION OF A SPACE
COLONY BELONGING TO THE UNION,
WHICH TOOK THE LEAD IN
SPACE DEVELOPMENT.
AN ENORMOUS ASTEROID FIELD
LIES ROUGHLY THREE HUNDRED
KILOMETERS AWAY,
MADE UP OF COUNTLESS
RESOURCE SATELLITES
WHICH WERE BROUGHT HERE FOR
COLONY CONSTRUCTION.
WITHIN THIS FIELD LIES
THE SECRET DOCK
OF THE PRIVATE ARMED
ORGANIZATION CELESTIAL BEING.
ALLELUJAH,
WHAT'S THE SITUATION LIKE?
NO PROBLEMS HERE.
GN PARTICLE DISPERSAL
AROUND THE SATELLITE
IS SHOWING NORMAL LEVELS.
YOU KNOW, YOU COULD'VE
LEFT THIS TO US
AND GONE DOWN
TO EARTH IF YOU WANTED.
I'M JUST FINE HERE.
MY BODY WAS DESIGNED
TO BE TOUGHER THAN OTHERS.
BESIDES, THERE ARE SOME THINGS
I WANT TO THINK OVER.
THE PROBLEM IS
WE'VE ALREADY BEGUN.
THIS ISN'T A CAREER THAT
HAS ROOM FOR REGRETS.
(Grunts)
YEAH, I KNOW THAT.
(Birds chirping)
Liu‐Mei:
WITH THE PROGRESS OF
NANO‐MACHINES
WE'VE REDUCED THE NEGATIVE
EFFECTS LIVING IN SPACE
CAN HAVE ON
THE HUMAN BODY.
HOWEVER,
WHEN IT COMES TO THE ISSUE
OF MENTAL HEALTH,
PEOPLE STILL NEED TO SPEND
SOME TIME ON THE GROUND.
IF YOU'RE TALKING ABOUT
LIVING IN SPACE
OUTSIDE OF COLONIES,
IT'S GOING TO TAKE
A LOT MORE TIME.
DO YOU DISAPPROVE OF HUMANITY
MOVING INTO SPACE,
MISS SUMERAGI?
AS A SPECIES,
I THINK WE'RE PROBABLY STILL
A LITTLE BIT IMMATURE.
BUT, THAT'S NOT REALLY
A BAD THING.
ONE OF LIFE'S GREATEST PLEASURES
IS DRINKING IN GRAVITY.
DRINKING THIS EARLY IS
UNHEALTHY YOU KNOW.
IT'S HARDER THAN
IT LOOKS TO KICK A HABIT.
I'M IMMATURE, TOO.
(Birds chirping)
Lichtendahl:
WHAT ARE THEY UP TO?
THOSE TWO THERE.
THEY'LL CALL YOU
A PEEPING TOM.
AND HIM,
WHO WANTS TO BE AROUND
SOMEONE SO FULL OF HIMSELF?
(Grunting)
THOSE ARE "ROSES".
HARO, WHAT ARE THOSE?
ANEMONES!
(Feldt chuckles)
EVERYONE'S
DOING THEIR OWN THING.
HEY, WHERE ARE THE MEISTERS?
SETSUNA WENT BACK TO
HIS APARTMENT,
LOCKON TOOK OFF
SOMEWHERE BY HIMSELF,
AND I THINK TIERIA
MIGHT BE DOWN IN THE BASEMENT.
YOU KNOW WHAT I'VE NOTICED?
A LACK OF TEAM SPIRIT.
YEAH, BUT IT WOULD BE WEIRD
TO HANG OUT WITH
EACH OTHER ALL THE TIME.
(Tieria thinking)
SINCE CELESTIAL BEING
BEGAN OPERATIONS,
CONFLICTS AROUND THE WORLD
HAVE DECREASED BY 38%.
63% OF CORPORATIONS
INVOLVED IN WEAPONS PRODUCTION
HAVE ANNOUNCED THEY WILL
LEAVE THE INDUSTRY.
IF WE GO STRICTLY BY
THESE NUMBERS,
WE'VE ACHIEVED VEDA'S
OPERATIONAL PREDICTIONS.
THE PROBLEM IS WE'VE EXPOSED
BOTH DYNAMES'S HIGH ALTITUDE
FIRING CAPABILITY
AND GN‐004 NADLEEH
TO THE WORLD.
AND THEN,
THERE'S SETSUNA F. SEIEI.
Setsuna:
WITH THE ASSISTANCE
OF THE UNITED NATIONS,
AZADISTAN HAS RESUMED
CONSTRUCTION
ON ITS SOLAR RECEIVER ANTENNAS.
(Girls talking)
Lockon:
OH, IT'S YOU, LICHTY.
I'VE BEEN CHECKING IN.
WHY ARE YOU CALLING?
AH...NO REASON.
BUT WAIT, IT SOUNDS LIKES
YOU'RE WITH SOME GIRLS!
HOW MANY CHICKS ARE YOU
HANGING OUT WITH, MAN?!
THAT DOG.
DON'T ASK
SUCH SILLY QUESTIONS.
IF THERE'S NOTHING ELSE
I'M HANGING UP. LATER.
NO, HOLD ON!
Girl #1:
WHICH ONE OF US
DO YOU LIKE BEST?
Girl #2:
I HOPE YOU LIKE ME BEST!
(Turns off recording)
Lockon:
IT LOOKS SO BEATIFUL NOW.
GREAT NEWS, KINUE!
YESTERDAY'S NEWS SPECIAL
HAD AN AUDIENCE SHARE
OF OVER 40%!
REALLY?!
THOSE ARE THE BEST AUDIENCE
NUMBERS THIS SHOW'S EVER HAD!
THEN, I CAN KEEP WORKING ON IT?!
YEAH! THE TOP GUYS
WANT YOU TO!
NEXT WE'LL GET YOU
WORKING ON THE EFFECT
CELESTIAL BEING'S ACTIVITIES
ARE HAVING ON THE WORLD ECONOMY!
TEAM UP WITH SAKAZAKI
FROM ECONOMICS AND
LIST THE COMPANIES THAT HAVE
EITHER GONE BANKRUPT‐‐
BUT BOSS!
PLEASE, LET ME
KEEP RESEARCHING AEOLIA!
WHAT'S THE POINT?!
(Disappointed sigh)
I'M STARTING
TO GET THE FEELING
THAT CELESTIAL BEING
MIGHT HAVE
A DIFFERENT GOAL THAN
SIMPLY ERADICATING WAR.
IF I KEEP RESEARCHING
AEOLIA SCHENBERG,
THERE'S A CHANCE I COULD
GET TO THE TRUTH HERE!
THAT'S WHAT I WANT TO DO!
(Grunts)
ALL RIGHT,
IT'S YOUR CALL!
JUST DON'T DO
ANYTHING RECKLESS.
DIG TOO DEEP AND YOU MIGHT NOT
BE ABLE TO CRAWL OUT.
YES, SIR.
WHEN YOU GET HOME,
SAY HI TO DAD FOR ME.
I'LL TELL HIM YOU'RE
DOING WELL
AND THAT
YOU'VE BEEN A GOOD GIRL.
(Grunts)
I'VE FINISHED LOADING
YOUR LUGGAGE MA'AM!
OH, THANKS SO MUCH,
SAJI!
HUH?
Saji:
HELLO!
I HAVEN'T SEEN YOU LATELY.
DID YOU GO OUT OF TOWN?
SOMETHING LIKE THAT.
Louise's Mom:
TAKE CARE!
BYE, MOM!
OH!
I KNOW IT'S OUT OF THE BLUE
BUT ARE YOU FREE TODAY?
WHY?
Saji:
I HAVE A FAVOR
I'D LIKE TO ASK YOU.
David:
MR. PRESIDENT,
HAVE YOU READ THE BRIEFING
CONCERNING PROJECT G?
UH‐HUH, I READ THEM.
TAKLAMAKAN.
THE HUMAN REFORM LEAGUE
HAS CHOSEN A REGION
WHERE THEY
BURIED ENRICHED URANIUM,
A RELIC OF THE PAST.
IT'S PERFECT FOR
A MILITARY EXERCISE, SIR!
IT'S SURROUNDED BY MOUNTAINS
IN ALL DIRECTIONS,
AND IT'S SO BARREN THAT
PEOPLE DON'T EVEN GO NEAR IT.
SINCE THEY CAN KEEP AWAY
ANY MEDIA,
IT'LL WORK FINE FOR THEM.
THEY'RE SO DESPERATE,
AREN'T THEY?
Official:
THAT'S THE MAXIMUM NUMBER OF
TROOPS MY NATION CAN DEPLOY.
WE'VE BEEN TAKING STRONG PUBLIC
CRITICISM SINCE MORALIA.
AND TO USE THAT ACCURSED GROUND
FOR THE EXERCISE...
BUT IF WE DON'T
DEPLOY OUR FORCES,
WE'LL END UP FALLING
BEHIND THE UNION
AND THE HUMAN REFORM LEAGUE.
THE PUBLIC WILL BE FINE,
IF WE CAN GET RESULTS.
WE MUST OBTAIN A GUNDAM.
NO MATTER THE COST.
IT TOOK A WHILE BUT
EVERYTHING IS NOW IN PLACE.
IF THIS OPERATION SUCCEEDS,
SIR, AND IT SHOULD,
OUR PARTY WILL STAY IN POWER
FOR THE NEXT 10 YEARS.
YOU HAVE TO LOOK
FURTHER INTO THE FUTURE.
TO ACHIEVE OUR GOAL OF BECOMING
THE LEADER OF THE WORLD
IT'S IMPERATIVE THAT
WE ACQUIRE THEM.
Howard:
OVER FLAGS?
THAT'S RIGHT. THE OFFICIAL TITLE
OF THE ANTI‐GUNDAM TASK FORCE.
ON THE SURFACE,
WE FUNCTION AS
THE EIGHTH INDEPENDENT
TACTICAL AIR SQUADRON,
CONSISTING
SOLELY OF FLAGS.
SO DOES THAT MEAN WE'RE
GETTING SOME MORE PILOTS?
WELL,
THAT'S WHY WE'RE HERE.
(Jets flying above)
HUH?
TWELVE MACHINES?!
Howard:
THE MARKINGS ON THAT MACHINE...
IS THAT JOSHUA FROM
ALASKA FLYING POINT?!
RANDY FROM GEORGIA,
AND STUART FROM ILLINOIS!
THEY'RE THE TOP PILOTS
FROM THEIR SQUADRONS.
THERE'S ANOTHER SURPRISE, TOO.
THE PLAN IS TO HAVE ALL
OF OUR FLAGS
CUSTOMIZED BY
PROFESSOR EIFMAN HIMSELF.
ARE YOU SERIOUS?!
WOULD I LIE TO YOU?
Graham:
OUR TASK FORCE IS PART
OF THE REGULAR MILITARY NOW
AND TWELVE FLAG FIGHTERS ARE
BEING TRANSFERRED HERE.
LOOKS LIKE THERE'S A BIG
OPERATION IN THE WORKS, BOYS.
KEEP YOUR HEADS UP!
Both:
ROGER THAT!
Peries:
ARE WE MOVING OUT, COLONEL?
MOST LIKELY.
THOUGH I HAVEN'T BEEN GIVEN
ALL THE DETAILS
OF THE OPERATION JUST YET.
Sergei:
I HEAR OTHER MOBILE SUIT TEAMS
BESIDES OURS
ARE GETTING THEIR
MARCHING ORDERS AS WELL.
THIS TIME, I WILL FOLLOW
YOUR ORDERS PRECISELY, SIR!
JUST RELAX.
YES, SIR!
(Woman moaning)
SORRY, BABE,
BUT DADDY'S GOT TO GO.
HA!
I'LL MAKE UP FOR IT NEXT TIME!
PATRICK COLASOUR,
AEU ACE IS HERE!
(Yelps in pain)
LIEUTENANT, YOU'RE LATE.
(Gasps)
DAMN YOU, WOMAN!
HITTING A MAN IN THE FACE
IS JUST‐‐
OWW!
YOU...YOU DID IT AGAIN!
I AM COLONEL
KATI MANNEQUIN
MISSION COMMANDER
OF THIS MOBILE SUIT TEAM.
(Grunts)
(Thinking)
SHE'S GORGEOUS!
I'M TERRIBLY SORRY FOR
BEING LATE, COLONEL!
I THINK I'M IN LOVE!
Alejandro:
THEY ACT LIKE THEY'RE MARTYRS.
IF THEY PERSIST IN THIS FASHION,
THEY'LL NEVER ERADICATE WAR.
PERHAPS THEY'VE MISTAKEN
THE ABILITIES OF THEIR GUNDAMS
FOR THE POWERS OF GOD.
THAT WOULD BE FOOLISH.
GUNDAMS ARE SIMPLY WEAPONS.
THEY WERE MADE TO ACHIEVE
CERTAIN OBJECTIVES,
AND THEY WERE
MADE FOR KILLING PEOPLE.
(Phone beeping)
HMM?
I'M GETTING A MESSAGE ON
THE CIVILIAN LINE?
HI, HOW'RE YOU DOING,
KUJO?
I HAVE SOME MATERIAL HERE THAT
I'D LIKE YOU TO LOOK OVER.
IF IT'S ALL RIGHT,
I'D LIKE TO GET YOUR OPINION.
HOPE TO HEAR FROM YOU SOON.
(Shocked gasp)
COULD THAT BE?!
NO WAY.
(Louise bawling)
MOM!
I KNEW THIS WOULD HAPPEN.
THANK YOU FOR COMING.
I'D HOPED IF WE HAD
MORE PEOPLE HERE,
LOUISE WOULD
HAVE BEEN DISTRACTED.
GUESS IT'S NOT
WORKING.
(Loud wailing)
YOUR MOTHER JUST WENT
BACK HOME, RIGHT?
SO WHY THE TEARS?
BECAUSE I MISS HER!
YOU CAN SEE HER
WHENEVER YOU WANT TO.
IT'S NOT LIKE SHE'S DEAD.
(Wails)
SAJI, I HATE THIS GUY!
EITHER PUNCH HIM
OR HIT HIM!
HEY, I CAN'T DO THAT!
AND PUNCHING AND HITTING
ARE THE SAME‐‐
(Crying continues)
(Sighs)
SORRY ABOUT THIS!
HUH?
YOU'RE SO PEACEFUL.
(PDA beeps)
I'M SORRY, SOMETHING
HAS JUST COME UP.
OH.
YEAH, GO HOME!
BIG JERK!
ALL THREE BLOCS ARE ON THE MOVE?
I SEE.
Christina:
A JOINT MILITARY EXERCISE?
Lichtendahl:
THE UNION, HRL AND AEU?
THAT IS WHAT
MY AGENTS REPORT.
THERE'LL BE AN OFFICIAL
ANNOUNCEMENT IN A FEW DAYS.
IF IT'S REALLY TRUE,
IT'LL BE ON A HUGE SCALE.
SO THE UNION AND HUMAN REFORM
LEAGUE ARE ALL FRIENDLY NOW?
WHAT'S THAT ABOUT?
IT'S BECAUSE OF US.
THAT WOULD BE
THE APPROPRIATE CONCLUSION.
THE HRL'S
CAPTURE OPERATION FAILED.
SO IF THEY WANT TO KEEP US
IN CHECK,
THEY'RE GOING TO HAVE TO WORK
WITH THE OTHERS TO PULL IT OFF.
BUT IF IT'S JUST
A MILITARY EXERCISE,
WE DON'T HAVE A GOOD REASON
TO INTERVENE, DO WE?
THERE'S MORE TO THIS.
Everyone:
HMM?
IT'S EXPENSIVE TO PUT
A LARGE FORCE IN THE FIELD.
THEY'RE NOT HOLDING
AN EXERCISE
OF THIS SCALE
TO KEEP US IN CHECK.
I AGREE WITH THAT.
WANG LIU MEI,
FIND OUT THE LOCATION, PLEASE.
IT'S BEING DONE.
KEEP ON IT.
EVERYONE, I THINK
WE'LL BE DEPLOYING YOU GUYS.
YOU SHOULD ENJOY YOURSELVES
WHILE YOU CAN.
(Determined grunt)
RIGHT, FELDT.
SHOPPING TIME! COME ON!
HEY!
YOU WANT TO‐‐
NO, I'LL PASS.
Lichtendahl:
BUT I DIDN'T SAY ANYTHING YET!
(Thinking)
WHO WOULD'VE THOUGHT THE WORLD
WOULD CHANGE SO QUICKLY?
IS THERE
A SHIFT IN HUMANITY THAT
NOT EVEN VEDA COULD PREDICT?
WE'VE GOT TO HURRY UP,
BUT BE CAREFUL OF THE G‐FORCES.
DON'T TREAT ME LIKE I'M OLD.
(Grunts)
SORRY ABOUT THAT.
Katagiri:
I'M GLAD YOU DECIDED TO COME.
Sumeragi:
WHAT DO YOU EXPECT,
AFTER SENDING ME
THAT DISTURBING FILE?
I DO APOLOGIZE FOR THAT.
SO, IS THIS FOR REAL?
HOW ABOUT I JUST CALL IT
THE MILITARY'S SIMULATION PLAN?
THE PROBABILITY
OF CAPTURING A GUNDAM
GIVEN CURRENT FORCE STRENGTH.
CAN I GET YOUR OPINION
AS A TACTICAL FORECASTER,
THAT IS?
THERE JUST ISN'T ENOUGH
DATA ON THE GUNDAMS.
AND NOT JUST THEIR
PERFORMANCE,
YOU CAN'T REALLY BE SURE
THERE ARE ONLY FOUR MACHINES.
I CAN'T IMAGINE MASS PRODUCTION.
THERE'D BE NO WAY TO HIDE ALL
THE PERSONNEL AND MATERIALS.
THAT'S TRUE.
LET'S SAY YOU'RE IN CHARGE OF
THIS OPERATION. NOW WHAT?
YOU ALREADY KNOW THE ANSWER.
YEAH, I KNOW.
WE CAN'T DEFEAT THEM
WITH OUR CURRENT FORCES.
BUT WHAT IF WE SURROUND THEM
WITH OVERWHELMING NUMBERS,
DRAW THE BATTLE OUT AND
SIMPLY EXHAUST THEIR PILOTS?
THERE'S THE CHANCE
THEY'D SWITCH TO AUTO‐PILOT
TO ENSURE SECRECY, OR EVEN
SELF‐DESTRUCT.
VERY ASTUTE.
YOU'VE BEEN FOLLOWING
CELESTIAL BEING
AND YOU HAVE ANALYZED THEM TOO.
HUH?
STOP IT.
DON'T SAY IT LIKE THAT.
SORRY.
(Surprised gasp)
Sumeragi:
DON'T WORRY.
I HAVEN'T COPIED THE FILE.
YOU KNOW, THIS PROVES YOU'RE
NOT MUCH OF A SOLDIER
IF YOU'RE SHARING THIS
WITH ME.
DID YOU WANT TO
DROP BY THE BASE?
PROFESSOR EIFMAN WAS WORRIED
ABOUT WHAT HAPPENED TO YOU.
NO, I'M SORRY.
I HAVE OTHER PLANS.
OH, IS SOMEONE WAITING
FOR YOU?
HUH?
AND IF THERE WAS?
WELL, THAT
WOULD MAKE ME JEALOUS.
I REALLY DO HAVE PLANS.
SEE YOU LATER.
THAT'S FINE.
I HOPE I DO SEE YOU.
Newscaster:
THIS NEWS JUST IN.
THE UNION, THE HUMAN
REFORM LEAGUE AND THE AEU
HAVE ANNOUNCED THAT ALL THREE
OF
THEIR ARMED FORCES
WILL TAKE PART IN A MASSIVE
MILITARY EXERCISE.
ACCORDING TO
AN OFFICIAL COMMENT
FROM A UNION
PUBLIC RELATIONS OFFICER,
THE GOAL OF THE EXERCISE
IS BETTER DEFENSE
OF THE ORBITAL ELEVATORS.
TO THIS END,
JOINT COUNTERMEASURES
WILL BE PRACTICED
DEALING WITH A WIDE‐RANGE OF
POSSIBLE SITUATIONS.
AT THIS TIME,
THE SCHEDULE AND LOCATION OF
THE EXERCISE ARE STILL UNKNOWN.
GUESS IT'S STARTED.
UH‐HUH.
Announcer:
IT'S BEEN DETERMINED THAT UNION
FORCES STATIONED IN JAPAN
WILL BE TAKING PART AND
THAT THE NATIONAL DEFENSE FORCE
HAS ALSO BEEN ASKED TO
PARTICIPATE.
HOWEVER, THE GOVERNMENT
HAS DECIDED TO ADOPT
A WAIT AND SEE ATTITUDE.
Howard:
HIGH‐OUTPUT PLASMA JETS AND
NEW MODEL LINEAR RIFLES.
NOW THAT'S WHAT A SQUADRON
SHOULD LOOK LIKE!
Daryl:
BUT IS IT
GOING TO DO ANY GOOD
WHEN WE GO UP AGAINST
THOSE GUNDAMS?
Joshua:
COWARDICE EVEN
BEFORE THE MISSION'S STARTED?
FIRST LIEUTENANT GRAHAM
CAN'T BE MUCH OF A LEADER
WITH SUBORDINATES LIKE THIS.
HE'S A CAPTAIN,
NOT A LIEUTENANT!
HE WAS PROMOTED FOR
THE NEW SQUADRON.
MY. HOW IMPRESSIVE.
DID HE KILL HIS
COMMANDING OFFICER AGAIN?
HOW DARE YOU SAY THAT CRAP!
(Chuckles)
YOU SHOULD BE CAREFUL.
IF YOU DON'T WATCH IT,
YOUR PRECIOUS CAPTAIN
COULD SHOOT YOU IN
THE BACK TOO.
YOU DIE!
Graham:
THAT'S ENOUGH.
Howard:
CAPTAIN!
I DON'T REALLY CARE
WHAT YOU THINK.
I PLAN TO CLEAR MY NAME
BY MY ACTIONS
ON THE BATTLEFIELD.
I LOOK FORWARD TO IT,
SQUADRON CAPTAIN GRAHAM AKER.
Hong‐Long:
MISTRESS. THE AMERICAN FLEET
IS ON THE MOVE.
IT APPEARS TO BE CROSSING
THE PACIFIC OCEAN
AND HEADING FOR EURASIA.
RIGHT NOW,
THE AEU SHOULD BE
ASSEMBLING
THEIR MOBILE SUIT TEAMS
AND HEADING FOR THE HUMAN
REFORM LEAGUE'S BORDERS.
BUT, HOW COULD YOU
KNOW THAT?
MISS SUMERAGI.
HER FORECASTS ARE VERY ACCURATE.
HOW DOES IT LOOK?
Sumeragi:
VEDA'S OPINION
MATCHES MINE.
SO YOU'RE BOTH PREDICTING
SOME KIND OF CONFLICT?
OH, MOST CERTAINLY.
WHERE?
Sumeragi: THE TAKLAMAKAN DESERT
IN NORTHWESTERN CHINA.
ENRICHED URANIUM IS STORED
UNDERGROUND THERE.
URANIUM?
I DON'T KNOW
WHICH ORGANIZATION IT IS,
BUT A TERRORIST GROUP IS
PLANNING TO ATTACK IT.
EITHER THE UNION OR
THE HRL LEAKED
THE INFORMATION
WHEN THEY CHOSE THIS SPOT.
IF THE FACILITY IS ATTACKED,
RADIOACTIVE MATERIAL
COULD LEAK OUT
AND CAUSE DAMAGE
ON A WORLDWIDE SCALE.
THEN WE'VE NO CHOICE
BUT TO INTERVENE.
YES, BUT WE'LL BE DIVING INTO
AN ENEMY MILITARY EXERCISE.
ALL OF THEIR FORCES WILL
IMMEDIATELY GO ON THE DEFENSIVE.
NO, THEY'RE GOING TO GO
ON THE OFFENSIVE
TO TRY TO CAPTURE THE GUNDAMS.
BUT WE'RE CELESTIAL BEING,
WE MUST ACT.
TIERIA.
TO A GUNDAM MEISTER, OUR SECRETS
AND MISSION OBJECTIVES
ARE MUCH MORE IMPORTANT
THAN LIFE OR DEATH.
ALL OF US ACCEPTED THAT
BEFORE PILOTING THE GUNDAMS.
IN FACT, WE COULDN'T DO THIS
WITHOUT THAT DETERMINATION.
Lockon:
ROGER. HEADING BACK
TO THE SAFEHOUSE.
THIS IS HEAVY STUFF.
THEY'RE NOT GOING TO HOLD US
BACK THIS TIME!
THIS IS THE WORLD'S RESPONSE.
MAXIMUM GN PARTICLE EMISSION!
DEPLOYING AHEAD OF MACHINE!
KYRIOS,
COMMENCING ATMOSPHERIC ENTRY!
Setsuna:
ROGER. WILL RENDEZVOUS
AT DESIGNATED TIME AND PLACE.
THANK YOU.
HUH?
WHAT THE?
WHY IS EXIA THERE?
Lasse:
HEY, SOMETHING WRONG?
OH, NOPE!
NOTHING WRONG HERE!
Lasse:
OKAY.
(Nervous giggle)
DARN.
HE'S OFF ON HIS OWN AGAIN.
Christina:
I DON'T CARE IF YOU
GET IN TROUBLE.
(Sleepy moan)
(Footsteps)
HMM?
(Footsteps continue)
I CAN HEAR YOU.
WHO'S THERE?
(Footsteps continue)
S‐SETSUNA F. SEIEI?
BUT WHY?
TELL ME, WHY IS
THIS WORLD SO TWISTED?
HUH?
IS IT GOD'S FAULT?
OR IS IT OURS?
(Gasps)
(Sighs)
I KNOW GOD IS FAIR.
AND PEOPLE HAVE OPEN HEARTS
BUT, THE WORLD STILL
BECOMES TWISTED BEYOND HOPE.
THAT'S WHY, WE HAVE TO LEARN
TO UNDERSTAND ONE ANOTHER‐‐
(Gasps)
SETSUNA.
(Thinking)
WHAT IS IT THAT'S TWISTED?
AND, WHERE IS IT?
COLONEL, THE PERSON
YOU'RE WAITING FOR IS HERE.
SEND HIM IN.
EXCUSE ME, COLONEL.
Al‐Saachez:
YOU HAVE A SECRET
MISSION FOR MY TEAM?
YOU'LL HAVE TO READ THE ORDERS
FOR THE DETAILS.
NOT EVEN I KNOW WHAT
THIS IS ALL ABOUT.
MY ROLE IN
THIS WHOLE ENDEAVOR,
IS TO SIMPLY HAND YOU
THOSE ORDERS THERE.
AND THEN TO GIVE YOU
THE AGRISSA.
AGRISSA.
THAT'S A MACHINE
THAT WAS USED IN THE FIFTH
SOLAR POWER WAR, WASN'T IT?
YOU'LL FIND
THE PICK‐UP POINT
FOR THE MACHINE
IN THE ORDERS AS WELL.
ROGER THAT, COLONEL.
LIEUTENANT GARY BIAGGI
OF THE FOURTH FOREIGN
MECHANIZED REGIMENT!
I ACCEPT THIS SECRET MISSION AND
AM COMMENCING IT IMMEDIATELY!
Al‐Saachez:
(Evil chuckle)
NOW THIS IS GOING TO BE FUN!
WE'RE TALKING WAR HERE!
AND ON A
GIGANTIC SCALE!
♪
Narrator:
OVERWHELMING NUMBERS,
AND A NEVER ENDING ASSAULT.
THIS IS THE WORLD'S RESPONSE.
THIS IS THE PLACE OF DEATH FOR
THE GUNDAM MEISTERS.
NEXT EPISODE:
"BROKEN WINGS".
SETSUNA SCREAMS
THE NAME OF HIS GOD.