WHAT THE?!
THOSE ARE PARTICLE BEAMS!
(Grunts)
A GUNDAM!
Johann:
IT'S THE GUNDAM EXIA!
EXIA HAS LOCATED THE TARGETS.
HAVE CONCLUDED THAT
THE THREE GUNDAM THRONE UNITS
ARE GUILTY OF
PROMOTING CONFLICT.
COMMENCING ARMED INTERVENTION.
EXIA WILL ELIMINATE TARGETS!
WHAT THE HELL DO YOU THINK
YOU'RE DOING?!
WE'RE ON THE SAME SIDE!
Setsuna:
WRONG.
HUH?
Setsuna:
THE THREE OF YOU
AND THOSE MACHINES OF YOURS
CANNOT POSSIBLY BE
GUNDAMS!
♪
(Metal clashing)
Nena:
WHAT... WHAT SHOULD
WE DO, JOHANN?!
COME IN, EXIA'S PILOT,
DO YOU READ ME?
WHY ARE YOU INTERFERING WITH US?
WE'RE DOING THIS TO
ERADICATE WAR.
Setsuna:
YOU'RE NOT!
YOU DON'T KNOW
WHAT IT MEANS TO BE A GUNDAM!
OBVIOUSLY YOU'RE CONFUSED, EXIA.
YOU CAN TAKE HIM OUT,
MICHAEL.
I ROGER THAT, JOHANN!
FANGS, FLY!
I'VE GOT MORE OF THEM!
(Growls)
(Surprised gasp)
BACKUP?
WHAT NOW?!
TIERIA ERDE'S HERE?!
VIRTUE!
READY TO DESTROY TARGETS!
Sumeragi:
EXIA IS FIGHTING THE THRONES?!
AND JUST NOW, VIRTUE SEEMS TO
HAVE JOINED THE BATTLE AS WELL.
TIERIA'S FIGHTING TOO?!
IT'S A DARK DAY WHEN GUNDAMS
FIGHT AMONGST THEMSELVES.
THEY COULD END UP
WIPING EACH OTHER OUT.
JUST LEAVE THEM ALONE,
OLD MAN.
YEAH, THE TRINITYS' BEHAVIOR
REALLY BUGS THE HELL OUT OF ME!
A SHAME HE'S SO
GOOD‐LOOKING.
THERE'S ALSO
THE REAL POSSIBILITY
THAT THEIR ACTIONS ARE
SOMEHOW PART OF THE PLAN.
AND MAYBE IT'S JUST
AS LIKELY THAT
WHAT WE'RE NOW DOING IN RESPONSE
IS PART OF THE PLAN AS WELL.
MISS SUMERAGI.
I'M GETTING AN URGENT CODED
MESSAGE FROM LOCKON STRATOS.
HE'S REQUESTING INSTRUCTIONS.
TELL HIM TO TRY TO STOP THE
GUNDAMS FROM FIGHTING IF HE CAN.
HOWEVER, I'LL RESPECT
HIS DECISION MAKING
IN RESPONSE TO WHATEVER'S
HAPPENING IN THE FIELD.
YES, MA'AM.
SO, WHAT YOU'RE REALLY
SAYING IS,
"YOU'RE JUST
GOING TO IMPROVISE."
SHAMEFUL FOR A
TACTICAL FORECASTER.
YOU GOT THAT RIGHT.
IT CERTAINLY IS.
HEY, ALLELUJAH,
ARE YOU LAUNCHING TOO?
NO, I'M GOING TO STAY HERE AND
PROTECT THE PTOLEMAOIS.
GIVEN WHAT'S HAPPENED, THIS SHIP
MIGHT BE IN DANGER TOO.
ALTHOUGH TRUTHFULLY,
I'M HAVING TO STOP MYSELF
FROM JOINING THEM.
MAN, THAT UNRULY BRAT
HAS A REAL KNACK
FOR DOING CRAZY THINGS.
LOCKON! YOU DIDN'T STOP HIM!
YOU DIDN'T STOP HIM!
YOU WERE SPYING ON US!
WELL, THANKS TO WHAT HE DID,
MISS SUMERAGI'S MIND WAS
MADE UP FOR HER!
BESIDES, YOU KNOW WHAT?
I KIND OF UNDERSTAND
HOW SETSUNA FEELS.
SEE, HE'S TRYING TO
BECOME A GUNDAM HIMSELF.
AN EMBODIMENT OF
THE ERADICATION OF WAR.
WHAT WILL YOU DO?
TO BE HONEST, I'M ITCHING
TO START SHOOTING!
HERE WE GO, HARO!
DYNAMES, LOCKON,
I'M TAKING OFF!
Liu‐Mei:
SO, EXIA IS OPPOSING
THE NEW GUNDAMS.
IS HE JUSTIFIED
IN TAKING THIS ACTION?
IT'S DIFFICULT TO SAY.
IF IT CHANGES THE WORLD,
WHAT THEY'RE DOING IS FINE
WITH ME, HONG LONG.
I DON'T REALLY CARE
WHAT THEIR METHODS ARE.
Ribbons:
A FIGHT BETWEEN GUNDAMS.
THIS IS SOONER THAN
I EXPECTED.
(Thinking)
WE'VE MOVED
INTO THE THIRD STAGE.
THERE'S NO TURNING BACK NOW.
ASSUME FORMATION S‐32.
Setsuna:
ROGER THAT.
THEY'RE IN A GN FIELD.
Nena:
JOHANN!
Michael:
WHY, YOU!
HUH. I HAVE TO ADMIT I NEVER
THOUGHT THE DAY WOULD COME
WHEN I'D BE
FIGHTING SIDE BY SIDE
IN FORMATION WITH YOU.
YEAH, ME TOO.
EXIA AND VIRTUE ARE
STILL ENGAGED
IN COMBAT WITH
THE THREE THRONES.
LOOKS LIKE THE TWO OF THEM ARE
USING TACTICAL FORMATIONS!
HUH?!
S‐32, D‐07,
AND EVEN F‐52.
THOSE TWO ARE COOPERATING.
NENA, DOCK WITH MY MACHINE.
Nena:
OKAY!
DO YOU REALLY THINK
WE'RE GOING TO GIVE YOU
TIME TO SET UP?!
WELL, THINK AGAIN!
TOO BAD YOU'RE NOT FAST ENOUGH!
I'VE GOT YOU LINED UP!
NADLEEH!
(High‐pitched whining)
WHAT THE...!
THE CONTROLS ARE FROZEN!
IT HURTS!
SYSTEM DOWN!
(Screaming)
(High‐pitched whining)
(Grunts)
WHAT HAPPENED?
(High‐pitched whining)
I CAN TAKE CONTROL
OF ALL MACHINES
THAT ARE LINKED WITH VEDA.
AND NOW YOU KNOW WHAT THE
GUNDAM NADLEEH'S TRUE POWER IS.
FOR I WAS THE ONLY ONE
WHO WAS GIVEN THIS POWER.
I CAN TRIGGER THE TRIAL SYSTEM
FOR GUNDAM MEISTERS!
Michael:
JOHANN! NENA!
(Grunts in pain)
Tieria: YOU HAVE BROUGHT
DISHONOR ONTO THE GUNDAM
MEISTERS!
AND FOR THAT
YOU DESERVE TEN THOUSAND DEATHS!
WHAT THE...?!
HUH?
(Machine whirring)
IT LOOKS LIKE THE TRIAL SYSTEM
WAS FORCIBLY DISENGAGED!
BUT HOW COULD THAT HAPPEN?!
(Gasps)
Tieria:
SOME OF THE DATA FROM
LEVEL SEVEN HAS BEEN ALTERED.
I WONDER WHAT THIS DATA COVERS.
(Gasps)
I'VE BEEN REJECTED?!
BUT IT'S ME!
HOW COULD I BE DENIED ACCESS?!
THAT MEANS VEDA'S BEEN‐‐
(Alarm beeps)
ANOTHER GUNDAM?!
THAT ONE'S DYNAMES!
AND NOW IT'S THREE ON THREE!
LET'S STICK TO
PLAYING FAIR NOW, PEOPLE!
LET'S SEE WHAT YOU'VE GOT!
Johann:
MICHAEL! NENA!
WE'RE WITHDRAWING!
OH, COME ON JOHANN,
ARE YOU FOR REAL?!
YEAH, WHY SHOULD WE RUN?!
IT'S ONLY GOING TO
HINDER THE PLAN
IF GUNDAMS START DESTROYING
EACH OTHER.
Michael:
(Growls)
ALL RIGHT, THEN!
YOU THREE RUNNING AWAY?
Johann:
YOU HAVE OTHER ENEMIES
YOU SHOULD BE DEALING WITH
BEFORE FIGHTING US.
ISN'T THAT RIGHT,
LOCKON STRATOS? OR IS THAT...
NEIL DYLANDY.
HIS NAME IS NEIL DYLANDY?
YOU BASTARD!
YOU'VE LOOKED AT MY DATA!
I'VE BEEN READING UP ON YOU,
WITH THE HELP OF VEDA.
(Gasps)
THAT'S THE INFORMATION
FROM LEVEL SEVEN!
OH, LOCKON.
YOU WERE LED TO BECOME
A GUNDAM MEISTER
BECAUSE YOU WANTED REVENGE
ON SOME PEOPLE
AND NOW ONE OF THEM IS
RIGHT NEXT TO YOU.
Lockon: (suspicious)
WHAT DO YOU MEAN?
Johann:
THE KPSA WAS A REBEL
GUERILLA GROUP
FROM THE REPUBLIC OF KRUGIS.
AMONG THEIR MEMBERS WAS
AN INDIVIDUAL
BY THE NAME OF SORAN IBRAHIM.
Lockon:
YEAH? SO WHAT,
WHO'S THAT?
SORAN IBRAHIM,
IS BETTER KNOWN BY THE CODENAME,
SETSUNA F. SEIEI.
(Surprised gasp)
YOU'RE ACCUSING SETSUNA
OF BEING‐‐
THAT'S RIGHT.
HE WAS A MEMBER
OF THE ORGANIZATION
THAT KILLED YOUR PARENTS
AND SISTER.
(Grunts)
HE IS ONE OF THOSE YOU SWORE
TO TAKE REVENGE AGAINST.
SETSUNA.
SEVEN
GUNDAM MACHINES.
THAT'S CORRECT,
SIR.
I DON'T KNOW WHAT ELSE WE CAN DO
TO STOP THOSE THINGS.
Official:
IF WE KEEP FIGHTING THEM
AND END UP EXHAUSTING
OUR MILITARIES,
OUR ECONOMIES
WOULD BE TOTALLY DEVASTATED!
AND THEN WE'D BE LEFT
WITH NO CHOICE
BUT TO ACCEPT THEIR TERMS
AND DISARM OURSELVES!
DON'T BE RIDICULOUS!
ACCEPTING THEIR TERMS
WOULD LEAD TO THE COLLAPSE
OF OUR NATIONAL IDENTITIES!
HUH?
YES, GO AHEAD.
Chairman:
WHAT IS IT?
IT SEEMS THAT SOMEONE CLAIMING
TO BE AFFILIATED WITH
CELESTIAL BEING HAS CONTACTED
US THROUGH THE NETWORK.
HUH.
DO YOU THINK IT'S LEGITIMATE?
THEY INCLUDED SOME DATA
RELATED TO THE ORGANIZATION.
WE'VE CONCLUDED
THIS PERSON IS FOR REAL.
HOW INTERESTING.
SEEMS THEY'RE DIVIDED
AMONGST THEMSELVES.
PERHAPS GOD HAS NOT
ABANDONED US AFTER ALL.
Ikeda:
THERE IS DEEP SORROW HERE
AMIDST THE RUBBLE
OF THE IRIS CORPORATION,
AS BEREAVED RELATIVES BEGIN
TO GATHER AT THE SITE.
THE MACHINES THAT CARRIED OUT
THE ATTACK
ARE THOUGHT
TO BE THREE NEW MODELS‐‐
DAMN GUNDAMS.
LOUISE, LOOK. SOME FLOWERS.
I'LL PUT THEM OVER HERE.
SAJI.
GO BACK TO JAPAN.
WHAT?
DON'T TAKE ANY MORE TIME OFF
FROM SCHOOL.
I'M SO HAPPY THAT
YOU COULD COME BE WITH ME.
BUT YOU KNOW YOU CAN'T
STAY HERE FOREVER.
COME ON,
I COULDN'T DO THAT!
I COULDN'T JUST GO AND
LEAVE YOU ALL ALONE!
SAJI, YOUR DREAM IS
TO WORK IN SPACE, RIGHT?
WELL LOOK, I DON'T WANT
YOUR LIFELONG DREAM
TO GO UNFULFILLED
BECAUSE I HELD YOU BACK.
YEAH, BUT‐‐
IF YOU STAY WITH ME,
THINGS WILL GET
DIFFICULT BETWEEN US.
I'LL ALWAYS FEEL GUILTY
ABOUT HOLDING YOU BACK,
AND YOU'LL REGRET ALL
THE THINGS YOU NEVER DID.
NO, THAT'S NOT TRUE!
(Sigh)
SAJI, CAN I ASK YOU TO
REALIZE MY DREAM FOR ME?
WHAT?
MY DREAM IS SIMPLE.
IT'S TO MAKE
YOUR DREAM COME TRUE.
SO, PLEASE, I NEED YOU TO
HELP ME FULFILL MY DREAM, SAJI.
OH, LOUISE.
(Sigh)
THEN IT'S A PROMISE.
♪
(Sleepy moan)
HMM?
YOU'RE GOING TO CATCH
YOUR DEATH OF COLD
IF YOU SLEEP ON THIS TABLE.
UH, WHAT?
UH, WHO ARE YOU?
A REAL GENTLEMAN
INTRODUCES HIMSELF FIRST.
WELL, I'M...I MEAN, HELLO,
MY NAME IS SAJI CROSSROAD.
I'M LOUISE HALEVY!
PLEASURE TO MEET YOU, SAJI!
WE'RE ON
A FIRST‐NAME BASIS?
AREN'T WE?
UH, WELL...I MEAN,
NOT THAT THERE'S ANYTHING
WRONG WITH IT.
THAT'S GOOD TO HEAR!
♪
SORRY TO ASK YOU TO DO
SOMETHING SO TEDIOUS.
I'M USED TO IT.
IT WAS LAGUNA HARVEY AFTER ALL.
OF COURSE IT WAS HIM.
HE RUNS A
LINEAR TRAIN COMPANY,
AND HEADS UP THEIR
INTERNATIONAL CARTEL.
THE MAN'S RICH.
HE'S GOT MORE THAN ENOUGH MONEY
TO BUILD MOBILE SUITS,
AND HE CONTROLS
THE ORBITAL ELEVATORS.
YOU KNOW WHAT THAT MEANS?
THE INVESTIGATION
JUST CAME TO A HALT.
WHY IS THAT?
WHA... WHAT ARE YOU
SERIOUS?
HE'S A MAJOR SHAREHOLDER
IN OUR COMPANY!
IF WE MESS WITH HIM
HE'LL SQUASH US.
THAT'S EXACTLY WHY
WE'LL KEEP IT TO OURSELVES.
YEAH, BUT‐‐
I'M NOT STOPPING NOW.
NOT WHEN I'VE FINALLY
FOUND MY FIRST CLUE.
MISS KINUE.
Lockon:
IS THAT TRUE, SETSUNA?
WERE YOU ACTUALLY
AFFILIATED WITH THE KPSA?
YEAH.
AND YOU'RE ORIGINALLY
FROM KRUGIS?
YES.
A CHILD GUERILLA SOLDIER.
LOCKON, LOOK.
ABOUT WHAT TRINITY SAID...
IT'S THE TRUTH.
BOTH OF MY PARENTS AND
MY LITTLE SISTER
WERE KILLED BY THE KPSA
IN AN ATTACK
BY A SUICIDE BOMBER.
IT ALL BEGAN WHEN
THE GLOBAL RESTRICTIONS
ON OIL EXPORTS
CAME INTO EFFECT,
RIGHT AFTER THE
SOLAR POWER GENERATION PLAN.
THEY SAID WE HAD TO STOP
DEPENDING ON
FOSSIL FUELS TO LIVE OUR LIVES.
BUT IT WAS THE
MIDDLE EASTERN COUNTRIES
THAT SUFFERED THE MOST.
THE EXPORT RESTRICTIONS
CRIPPLED THEIR ECONOMIES
AND THEIR CITIZENS WERE
PLUNGED INTO POVERTY.
THE POOR TURNED TO THEIR GOD
AND OPENED THEIR EARS TO
HIS SELF‐PROCLAIMED SPOKESMEN.
THEY WERE INFLUENCED BY
DESPICABLE PEOPLE
WHO SOUGHT ONLY
WEALTH AND POWER!
AND SO, THIS LED TO THE
SOLAR POWER WARS
THAT WOULD LAST
FOR OVER TWENTY YEARS.
FOR THOSE LIVING IN THE
LAND OF GOD IT WAS A HOLY WAR,
A SELFISH PRETEXT.
OF COURSE YOU CAN SAY
THE SAME THING
ABOUT THE UN AND
THEIR EXPORT RESTRICTIONS.
BUT IT ISN'T GOD OR RELIGION
THAT WAS AT FAULT HERE.
AND NEITHER WAS THE
SOLAR POWER GENERATION SYSTEM.
BUT SOMEHOW, THE WORLD BECAME
TWISTED BECAUSE OF THESE THINGS.
I KNOW THAT MUCH ANYWAY.
AND I UNDERSTAND YOU WERE
JUST BEING USED BY THE KPSA,
AND THAT YOU WERE FIGHTING
A BATTLE THAT YOU NEVER WANTED.
BUT I WAS DRAGGED INTO
THAT TWISTED WORLD
AND I LOST MY FAMILY!
I LOST THEM.
IS THAT THE REASON WHY
YOU ACCEPTED THE OFFER
TO BECOME A MEISTER?
YEAH, THAT'S THE REASON.
AND I REALIZE I'M
A WALKING CONTRADICTION.
NOW I'M DOING THE SAME THINGS
A TERRORIST DOES.
INSTEAD OF CUTTING
THE CHAIN OF VIOLENCE,
I MADE THE CHOICE
TO FIGHT BACK.
BECAUSE I SINCERELY
BELIEVE THAT
THE WORLD NEEDS TO BE CHANGED
FROM ITS VERY FOUNDATIONS
SO THAT A TRAGEDY LIKE THAT
NEVER HAPPENS AGAIN.
IF ONLY I HAD SOMETHING
SO POWERFUL
IT COULD SERVE AS
A DETERRENT TO THE WORLD.
THAT'S A GUNDAM.
I WILL ACCEPT MY PUNISHMENT
FOR NOT STOPPING THE KILLING
AFTER I'VE CHANGED THE WORLD.
BUT BEFORE THAT HAPPENS
THERE'S SOMETHING I HAVE TO DO.
LOCKON, WAIT!
SETSUNA, I WANT TO SHOOT YOU
SO VERY BADLY RIGHT NOW.
LET ME AVENGE MY FAMILY.
LET ME SETTLE THIS SCORE.
(Gunshot)
AT ONE TIME,
I USED TO BELIEVE IN GOD.
I WAS FORCED TO BELIEVE.
AND SO YOU THINK THAT MEANS
YOU'RE NOT RESPONSIBLE?
BUT IN THIS WORLD
THERE IS NO GOD.
Setsuna's mother:
WHY?
WHY ARE YOU DOING THIS, SORAN?
(Sobbing)
GOD DOES NOT EXIST,
NOT IN THIS WORLD.
THAT'S NOT A
GOOD ENOUGH ANSWER!
I BELIEVED IN GOD,
AND THEN FOUND OUT THAT
HE DIDN'T EXIST.
ALL BECAUSE OF ONE MAN.
AND WHICH MAN IS THAT?
HE WAS THE LEADER
OF THE KPSA.
ALI AL‐SAACHEZ.
WHO IS THIS ALI AL‐‐
‐‐SAACHEZ PERSON?
Setsuna:
HE WAS WORKING
FOR THE PMCS IN MORALIA.
Tieria:
THE PRIVATE MILITARY
COMPANIES?
FIRST A GUERILLA THEN
A MERCENARY?!
WHAT IS THIS GUY, SOME KIND OF
A DAMNED WAR JUNKIE?!
ON THE BATTLEFIELD OF MORALIA,
I SAW HIM AGAIN.
THAT'S WHY.
WHY YOU LEFT YOUR COCKPIT
THAT TIME.
I WANTED TO MAKE SURE
IT REALLY WAS HIM.
I WANTED TO KNOW WHERE
HIS GOD WAS!
AND, IF THERE WAS NO GOD
INSIDE HIM,
ALL THIS TIME...
I JUST...
SETSUNA.
Lockon:
SETSUNA!
LET ME ASK YOU ONE QUESTION.
WHAT DO YOU WANT TO
ACHIEVE WITH EXIA?
I'LL ERADICATE WAR!
YOU WON'T BE ABLE TO
IF I SHOOT YOU!
I DON'T MIND.
YOU COULD DO IT
INSTEAD OF ME.
CHANGE THIS TWISTED WORLD
IN MY PLACE.
BUT WHILE I'M ALIVE
I'LL KEEP FIGHTING.
AND NOT AS POOR SORAN IBRAHIM,
BUT AS CELESTIAL BEING'S
GUNDAM MEISTER.
AS SETSUNA F. SEIEI.
PILOTING A GUNDAM?
Setsuna:
YES.
I AM...
GUNDAM.
(Chuckles)
CRAZY, I DON'T WANT TO
SHOOT YOU ANYMORE!
YOU REALIZE YOU'RE AN IMPOSSIBLE
GUNDAM NUT, DON'T YOU?
THANK YOU.
HUH?
TO ME, THAT'S
A GREAT COMPLIMENT.
(Laughing)
HMM.
SO, THIS IS BEING HUMAN?
Johann:
I NEVER THOUGHT WE'D COME
UNDER ATTACK FROM GUNDAMS.
AH, THEY MUST HAVE GONE
CRAZY OR SOMETHING!
AND TO THINK
I ACTUALLY KISSED HIM!
WE'LL ASK LAGUNA
FOR INSTRUCTIONS.
DEPENDING ON THE SITUATION,
WE MAY END UP
FIGHTING GUNDAMS AGAIN.
HELL YEAH!
I SAY BRING THEM ON!
(Impressed murmuring)
♪
Narrator:
SIGNIFICANT CHANGES TO THE PLAN
HAVE DRAMATICALLY ALTERED
THE BALANCE OF THE WORLD.
IT SEEMS PEOPLE
ONLY HAVE A CHOICE
BETWEEN SHEDDING TEARS,
FIGHTING OR DYING.
NEXT EPISODE:
"BLADE OF REFORMATION".
WHO WILL THIS SUFFERING AFFECT?