WHAT ARE THE ODDS?
YOU AND I MEETING
LIKE THIS.
YOU KNOW, BEING
A SENTIMENTAL VIRGO AND ALL,
I CAN'T HELP FEELING WE WERE
DESTINED TO MEET.
OR PERHAPS
I FOUND YOU BECAUSE
YOU JUST STOPPED EMITTING
THOSE LIGHT PARTICLES.
THAT'S PROBABLY IT!
(Groans)
HE FORCED ME BACK.
HOLD ON!
GOOD LUCK HITTING ME WITH
THAT BIG BLADE OF YOURS!
HE DODGED IT!
BEFORE I LEAVE...
I THINK I'LL COLLECT
A LITTLE SOUVENIR!
DON'T YOU...TOUCH ME!
(Grunts)
(Shots firing)
(Slash)
HE HAS A BEAM SABER?
(Groans)
♪
Narrator:
2307 A. D.
THE PRIVATE ARMED ORGANIZATION,
CELESTIAL BEING,
DECLARES THAT IT WILL
ELIMINATE
ALL WARS AROUND THE WORLD.
SUBSEQUENTLY, IT BEGINS ITS
ARMED INTERVENTIONS.
AFTER SHOCKING
THE WORLD BY INTERVENING
IN THE CEYLON ETHNIC CONFLICT
IN SOUTHERN INDIA,
THE GUNDAM MEISTERS
RECEIVE ORDERS
FOR A NEW MISSION.
IS THIS GOD'S JUDGMENT
VISITED UPON HUMANITY...
OR IS IT THE PRECURSOR
TO A REVOLUTION?
Katagari:
MY, OH MY, YOU ARE
UNPREDICTABLE AREN'T YOU?
I WENT AND
LOST MY RIFLE.
I'LL WRITE UP
AN APOLOGY.
AH, I WOULDN'T
WORRY ABOUT THAT
IF I WERE YOU GRAHAM.
THE DATA WE COLLECTED
ON THE GUNDAM
MADE THE TRADE
A GOOD ONE.
HECK, IT WOULD HAVE
BEEN WORTH LOSING
THE FLAG ALTOGETHER.
THE PAINT
YOU SCRAPED OFF IT
WHEN YOU MADE CONTACT
COULD GIVE US SOME
GOOD LEADS.
THAT CELESTIAL BEING
PILOT...
I KEEP THINKING
ABOUT HOW YOUNG HE WAS.
YOU TALKED TO HIM?
OF COURSE NOT.
HE SIGNALED HIS EMOTIONS
THROUGH THE WAY
HIS MOBILE SUIT MOVED.
(Ringing)
Officer:
WE'VE LOST THE GUNDAM, SIR.
WE GOT DUMPED.
LAUNCHING ALONE
LIKE THAT...
WHO WAS IN THAT FLAG?
Journalist: ANYTHING FROM OUR
REPORTER ON THE SCENE?! YEAH,
UH‐HUH, NOTHING YET!
A GUNDAM! EVEN IF IT'S A SMALL
CLIP I WANT TO SEE A GUNDAM!
STILL NO STATEMENT
FROM CELESTIAL BEING!
NEWS UPDATE IN
TEN MINUTES, PEOPLE!
WE'LL BE BROADCASTING LIVE
FROM THE SCENE!
EXCUSE ME, CHIEF...
AND THE HUMAN
REFORM LEAGUE CHAIRMAN'S
GOT A STATEMENT COMING
SO KEEP A SLOT OPEN!
HERE'S
THE FIRST DRAFT!
RIGHT.
UM, KINUE'S ON‐‐
NOT NOW, KID!
AEOLIA SCHENBERG....
A SCIENTIST
AND LEGENDARY INVENTOR
FROM THE LATE 21ST CENTURY.
HE PROPOSED
THE BASIC THEORY
OF THE SOLAR POWER
GENERATION SYSTEM.
HE RARELY APPEARED IN PUBLIC
AND NOTHING EXCEPT HIS FAME
IS REMEMBERED NOW.
GIVEN HIS GENIUS AND WEALTH,
I COULD SEE
HIM BEING THE PERSON
BEHIND THE CREATION OF
CELESTIAL BEING.
BUT WHY ARE THEY MAKING
THEIR MOVE NOW?
OVER TWO HUNDRED YEARS LATER?
SCHENBERG'S BLOODLINE
ENDED WITH HIM.
HE HAS NO HEIRS.
I SEE. AND WHAT
HAPPENED TO HIS FORTUNE?
THERE'S NOTHING ABOUT
IT IN THE RECORDS.
HE PROBABLY HAD
A HAND IN THAT DETAIL.
SECURITY WAS PRETTY MUCH
NONEXISTENT
BACK IN
THE 21ST CENTURY.
YES, SIR.
CELESTIAL BEING HAS
BEEN SURPRISINGLY METICULOUS.
MR. SECRETARY,
DO YOU THINK
THEY'LL CONTINUE
THEIR ARMED INTERVENTIONS?
I WOULD,
IF I WERE THEM.
PREPARE THE APPROPRIATE
MATERIALS
FOR OUR REPORT
TO THE ASSEMBLY.
AND OUR EXCUSES.
Announcer:
PASSENGERS BOARDING
HEAVEN'S PILLAR
TRAVEL BUREAU NUMBER E‐273,
PLEASE
PROCEED TO GATE A12.
HMM?
HEY, YOU KNOW HOW LATE
YOU ARE?
UNRULY BRAT.
I ASSUMED
YOU WERE DEAD.
DID SOMETHING
HAPPEN?
I SUBMITTED
MY REPORT TO VEDA.
PERHAPS I'LL HAVE
A LOOK AT IT LATER.
SURE.
ANYWAY, THE IMPORTANT
THING IS WE'RE ALL SAFE.
I'LL LEAVE SPACE
TO YOU, TIERIA.
WE'RE GOING TO GET READY
FOR OUR NEXT MISSION.
I'LL FOLLOW THE ORDERS.
THOUGH I HAVE
MY DOUBTS.
(Both chuckle)
HERE ARE YOUR
ORDERS.
ENJOY YOUR DRINKS,
GENTLEMEN.
IT'S MILK.
THIS ONE'S ON ME.
Allelujah:
BUT, DO YOU REALLY THINK
IT'LL WORK?
USING THE ELEVATOR
TO GET A UNIT BACK INTO SPACE?
Lockon:
NOTHING TO WORRY ABOUT.
IT'S MIXED IN WITH
THE COLONY CONSTRUCTION
MATERIALS, AS PLANNED.
AS LONG AS
IT'S THE SAME WEIGHT
AND IT GETS THROUGH
BOARDING,
THERE ARE NO CHECKS AFTER THAT.
ESPECIALLY HERE.
THAT'S DEFINITELY
THEIR ACHILLES HEEL.
AND IF WE HAVE A WEAK POINT
OF OUR OWN...
I GUESS IT WOULD BE THE FACT
THAT WITHOUT THE GUNDAMS,
THE PTOLEMAOIS'S
OPERATING TIME
IS SEVERELY LIMITED
WITH ONLY
FOUR SOLAR REACTORS.
DON'T TALK ABOUT
OUR SECRETS.
RIGHT, MY MISTAKE.
TIERIA'S TRAIN IS
LEAVING NOW.
Announcer:
HEAVEN'S PILLAR TRAVEL
BUREAU NUMBER E‐277
NOW DEPARTING
ON SCHEDULE AT 14:18...
(Thinking)
A LINEAR TRAIN TO SPACE.
I CAN FINALLY GET BACK.
I HATE THE SURFACE.
ALRIGHT THEN,
LET'S GO HOME!
I WISH WE COULD TAKE
A BIT OF A BREAK.
GOT TO STRIKE WHILE
THE IRON'S HOT.
THE WORLD'S NOT GOING TO
LISTEN TO US
THE FIRST FEW TIMES AROUND.
GOOD DAY, COLONEL,
WE'VE BEEN WAITING FOR YOU.
AND HOW DID SPACE
TREAT YOU, SIR?
I FIND THERE'S SOMETHING
COMFORTING ABOUT GRAVITY.
I AGREE, SIR.
THE COMMANDER HAS BEEN
WAITING FOR YOU.
THIS WAY.
I'D LIKE TO
STOP BY CEYLON FIRST.
BUT, SIR,
IF WE DO THAT‐‐
I ONLY BELIEVE
IN THINGS
THAT I'VE SEE WITH
MY OWN TWO EYES.
THE COMMANDER
WILL UNDERSTAND.
SIR!
I WILL JOIN YOU!
YOU WERE THERE TO
SEE THE A. E. U.'S NEW MODEL.
BUT INSTEAD OBSERVED
A HUGE MESS.
I WAS THERE AND I STILL
CAN'T BELIEVE
A MACHINE
LIKE THAT EXISTS.
I THINK IT'S WELL WORTH OUR
TIME TO RESEARCH IT.
THE TOP BRASS
FEEL THE SAME WAY.
Both:
HUH?
BECAUSE YOU TWO HAVE ACTUALLY
SEEN THIS GUNDAM
YOU'VE BOTH
RECEIVED TRANSFERS.
ANTI‐GUNDAM
INVESTIGATIVE...
TASK FORCE?
A NEWLY FORMED TEAM.
COMMAND WILL GIVE IT
AN OFFICIAL NAME LATER.
PROFESSOR RALPH EIFMAN.
YOU MEAN HE'S
GOING TO BE
OUR CHIEF
TECHNOLOGIST?
AN INDICATOR OF HOW SERIOUS
THE BRASS THINKS THIS IS.
DEAL WITH IT IMMEDIATELY.
SIR!
LIEUTENANT GRAHAM AKER.
TECH ADVISOR
KATAGIRI.
TRANSFERRING
TO THE ANTI‐GUNDAM
INVESTIGATIVE
TASK FORCE!
THAT WAS A SURPRISE.
DID YOU FORESEE THAT
HAPPENING?
MY GOD‐LIKE POWERS
MUST BE SLIPPING.
ALTHOUGH I DO FEEL
FATE IS AT WORK HERE.
Professor:
THOUGH SPORADIC,
TERRORIST ACTIVITY
IN THE ULSTER REGION
OF IRELAND HAS CONTINUED
FOR ALMOST
FOUR CENTURIES.
IT IS BELIEVED TO HAVE
ORIGINATED WITH A CONFLICT
BETWEEN TWO CHRISTIAN
DENOMINATIONS,
THE CATHOLICS
AND THE PROTESTANTS,
BUT THAT IS NOT
THE ONLY ISSUE DIVIDING THEM
FOR THIS TERM PAPER,
YOU ARE TO USE THE NORTHERN
IRELAND CONFLICT MAP...
(Sighs)
ANOTHER PAPER?
WHY DO WE NEED
A HISTORY CREDIT
IF WE'RE ENGINEERING
MAJORS?
FURTHER TECHNOLOGICAL
INNOVATIONS WILL BE BASED
UPON ORBITAL ELEVATOR
MAINTENANCE
AND THE DEVELOPMENT
OF SPACE COLONIES.
A SENSE OF HISTORY
IS REQUIRED
IN ORDER TO
RELATE TO ENGINEERS
FROM OTHER NATIONS
(Giggles)
HE SAID THAT
IN THE FIRST CLASS!
YEAH, I KNOW THAT,
BUT STILL...
I MEAN, THAT'S WHY
THEY LET ME COME HERE
AS AN EXCHANGE
STUDENT.
AND I SURE DO
APPRECIATE THAT.
REALLY?
HUH?
MY STUDY EXCHANGE
IS GOING TO END
IN TWO YEARS.
WHAT ARE WE
TALKING ABOUT HERE?
HEY, DO YOU EVER
THINK ABOUT THE FUTURE, SAJI?
YEAH, I GUESS.
WHEN YOU DO...
AM I IN IT?
YEAH, I GUESS.
AUGH!
WHAT?
H‐HEY, WHAT'S UP?
LOUISE!
AH, GIRLS CAN
BE SO‐‐
THIS IS WHERE
YOU'RE SUPPOSED TO CHASE ME!
OH! RIGHT!
A SOFT DRINK?
THEY SERVE AN ORIGINAL
COCKTAIL HERE
THAT I HIGHLY RECOMMEND.
I'M STILL A MINOR,
YOU KNOW.
OH, DO
EXCUSE ME.
I'LL HAVE THE USUAL.
YES, SIR.
THE THIRD MISSION IS
ABOUT TO GET UNDERWAY.
IF YOU PLAN ON FOLLOWING
THE ACTION,
I SUGGEST YOU THINK
ABOUT SETTING UP THREE MONITORS.
AH, I SIMPLY CAN'T WAIT.
I'LL BE SURE TO FOLLOW
YOUR SUGGESTION.
YOU LIKE TO WATCH?
(Groans)
THIS WAY, COLONEL.
SO, THAT'S IT.
HAVE YOU LEARNED
ANYTHING YET?
YES. YOU THERE!
GIVE COLONEL SERGEI
HERE THE DETAILS.
YES, SIR.
IT'S AN OPTIONAL
BOMBING MODULE
FOR A MOBILE SUIT
MADE OUT OF E‐CARBON.
THE MATERIAL'S STATE
OF THE ART,
BUT WE HAVEN'T
FOUND ANY EVIDENCE
OF NEW TECHNOLOGY
IN ITS CONSTRUCTION, SIR.
AND WHAT ABOUT
THE MISSILES INSIDE?
RIGHT. AFTER STUDYING
THE RESIDUE,
WE'VE DETERMINED
THEY WERE OF
THE THREE HUNDRED
KILOGRAM GUIDED TYPE.
BY THE WAY,
NO COUNTRY OR MANUFACTURER
PRODUCES THIS TYPE.
THEY'RE PRODUCING THEM
ON THEIR OWN.
Katagiri:
JUDGING FROM THE IMPACT
YOUR MACHINE TOOK,
I BELIEVE THE GUNDAM'S OUTPUT
IS ROUGHLY
SIX TIMES
THAT OF THE FLAG'S.
I WONDER WHAT
KIND OF ENGINE IT USES...
Sergei:
IT HAS A LOT OF POWER,
BUT AT THE SAME TIME,
SO AGILE.
YES, THE COMBAT
DATA CONFIRMS THAT.
AND THERE'S ONLY
ONE FACTOR
THAT MAKES THAT
MOBILITY POSSIBLE.
THAT LIGHT?
YES. APPARENTLY
THE GUNDAM'S BODY
EMITTED GLOWING
PARTICLES OF SOME KIND.
THAT EXPLAINS SOME
OF MY QUESTIONS.
IT MUST BE WHY
THEY WEREN'T PICKED UP
BY OUR RADAR OR SENSORS.
YEAH, THOSE PARTICLES
AREN'T ONLY USED FOR STEALTH,
BUT ALSO FOR CONTROLLING
THE MACHINE.
MORE THAN LIKELY
THEY'RE ALSO UTILIZED
IN ITS WEAPONRY.
PROFESSOR
RALPH EIFMAN!
WHAT A REMARKABLE MAN.
HE POSSESSES TECHNOLOGY SEVERAL
DECADES IN ADVANCE OF OURS.
AEOLIA SCHENBERG....
HE'S THE
HISTORICAL FIGURE
WHO APPEARED IN
CELESTIAL BEING'S
STATEMENT
OF RESPONSIBILITY.
YES, I KNOW THE NAME.
HE PROPOSED THE SOLAR POWER
GENERATION SYSTEM.
INTELLIGENCE IS
FOLLOWING THAT ANGLE
IN ITS
GUNDAM INVESTIGATION.
THEY WON'T FIND
ANYTHING DOWN THAT PATH.
THEY COULD THROW AWAY
THIS MODULE
BECAUSE THEY
DON'T HAVE TO
KEEP THIS
TECHNOLOGY SECRET.
Eifman:
WHAT I'D REALLY LIKE TO DO
IS FOCUS ON CAPTURING
A GUNDAM.
IF IT'S POSSIBLE.
I COMPLETELY AGREE.
AND THAT'S WHY
I WANT THIS MACHINE MODIFIED.
WHAT ABOUT THE STRESS
ON THE PILOT?
DON'T WORRY ABOUT
THE PILOT'S SAFETY.
HOWEVER, I'D LIKE YOU
TO GET IT DONE IN ONE WEEK.
OH? YOU DON'T ASK
FOR MUCH DO YOU?
IF WE'RE COURTING
A GUNDAM,
WE'LL HAVE TO
BE A LITTLE AGGRESSIVE
HE THINKS HE'S FALLEN
IN LOVE WITH IT.
(Phone rings)
YEAH, IT'S ME.
WHAT? THE GUNDAMS
ARE BACK?
LOCATION?
SIR! THERE
ARE TWO LOCATIONS!
TWO PLACES?
SIMULTANEOUSLY?
IN SOUTH AFRICA?
MOST LIKELY,
THEY'RE INTERVENING
IN THE CIVIL WAR OVER
THE MINING RIGHTS
TO THE COUNTRY'S
MINERAL DEPOSITS.
AUGH, I HATE THIS.
THIS FEELS WAY TOO MUCH
LIKE BEING A BULLY.
COME ON,
HURRY UP AND DISARM.
I'LL START HITTING YOU...
(Shots firing)
THEY RAN! THEY RAN!
HEY, THEY WISED UP!
GOOD STUFF!
Eifman:
DON'T DO IT!
AND WHY NOT?
ONE'S IN TARIBIA!
WE CAN GET THERE
FROM HERE!
I HAVE A DEEP‐ROOTED
LOATHING
FOR ILLEGAL
NARCOTICS.
IF THEY'RE GOING TO
BURN IT DOWN
THEN I'M MORE
INCLINED TO HELP THE GUNDAMS!
NARCOTICS...
THEY'RE PLANNING ON
DESTROYING THE REASON
FOR THE WAR ITSELF.
Allelujah:
THIRTY MINUTES HAVE ELAPSED
SINCE BEGINNING CIRCLING
MANEUVER.
WARNING COMPLETE.
KYRIOS, NOW COMMENCING
MISSION OPERATIONS.
(Boom)
(People gasp)
NINETY‐SEVEN PERCENT
OF OBJECTIVE ACHIEVED.
MISSION COMPLETE.
MISSIONS LIKE THIS ONE
ARE A PLEASURE.
A THIRD UNIT JUST
APPEARED HERE ON CEYLON?
YES, SIR!
GARRISON POST SEVEN!
IS THERE A TIEREN
I CAN USE?
I'LL HEAD OUT.
YOU'RE GOING
IN PERSON, COLONEL?!
I ALREADY TOLD YOU,
I ONLY BELIEVE
IN SOMETHING
AFTER I'VE SEEN IT
WITH MY OWN EYES.
WE JUST
LOST NUMBER THREE!
THIS GUNDAM THING'S
A MONSTER!
EXIA CONTINUING
CONFLICT INTERVENTION.
ELIMINATING TARGETS.
Soldier:
FIRE! FIRE!!
IT'S TOO FAST!
(Crash)
(Slash)
FIRST PHASE COMPLETE.
(Beeping)
(Boom)
REINFORCEMENTS?
SO, THAT'S A GUNDAM.
(Thud)
NO RIFLE?
IS HE TESTING ME?
SHOW ME YOU'RE SERIOUS ABOUT
ELIMINATING WAR.
(Slash)
HE'S TAKEN THE BAIT!
(Grunts)
HMPH!
THAT HEAD OF YOURS...
I'M TAKING IT!
(Beeping)
(Grunts)
YOU'RE MISTAKEN!
(Screaming)
(Yelling)
NO ONE TOUCHES ME.
NOW ARRIVING
AT RENDEZVOUS POINT.
Christina:
VISUAL CONFIRMATION OF VIRTUE.
Feldt:
PREPARE FOR DOCKING.
RELATIVE GUIDANCE SYSTEM
ACTIVATED.
CONTAINER, OPEN.
LINKAGE SYSTEM IS CLEAR.
VIRTUE NOW ENTERING SHIP.
(Buzzing)
(Clang)
Feldt:
DOCKING COMPLETE.
BEGIN CONNECTING VIRTUE'S
G. N. DRIVE TO PTOLEMAOIS.
Christina:
READY FOR ENERGY TRANSFER
FROM VIRTUE TO PTOLEMY.
COMMENCING TRANSFER.
SPACE IS MUCH BETTER.
GOOD WORK.
HOW'D THE MISSIONS GO?
WENT OFF WITHOUT
A HITCH.
HURRY UP, WE'LL
CELEBRATE WITH A DRINK.
I RESPECTFULLY DECLINE.
(Sumeragi sighs)
YOU'RE NO FUN.
HUH?
HEY! I GUESS
WE'RE NEIGHBORS.
MY NAME'S
SAJI CROSSROAD.
I LIVE HERE WITH
MY BIG SISTER.
SETSUNA F. SEIEI.
SEIEI?
THAT'S AN UNUSUAL NAME.
NICE TO MEET YOU.
(Door unlocks)
NOT TOO SOCIABLE.
I'M HOME. HMM?
WHAT'S UP?
WORK?
YEAH THEY
CALLED ME IN.
I'VE BEEN PRETTY
BUSY LATELY,
THANKS TO
CELESTIAL BEING.
THAT AGAIN?
MAKE YOURSELF SOME
DINNER. SEE YOU.
RIGHT...
(Phone ringing)
Louise:
HELLO, SAJI?!
LOUISE?
WHAT'S THE MATTER?
TURN ON THE NEWS!
WHAT'S UP?
JUST TURN IT ON!
AND WE HAVE SOME BREAKING NEWS
FROM NORTHERN IRELAND TODAY.
AT DAYBREAK, THE TERRORIST
ORGANIZATION, REAL I. R. A.,
ANNOUNCED THAT IT WILL
CEASE ALL TERROR ACTIVITIES.
Correspondent:
THIS MEANS THE CONFLICT
IN NORTHERN IRELAND
THAT HAS CONTINUED FOR ALMOST
FOUR HUNDRED YEARS...
HAS COME TO AN END.
SO NOW A NEW PATH
TO PEACE HAS BEEN OPENED.
WAIT, BUT THAT MEANS...
Louise:
ISN'T THIS AMAZING?
I WONDER HOW
IT'S GOING TO AFFECT
THE TERM PAPER WE'VE
GOT TO WRITE
ON TODAY'S LESSON?
THE WORLD IS...
THE WORLD IS CHANGING.
♪
Narrator:
SOME COUNTRIES TAKE ADVANTAGE
OF CELESTIAL BEING.
ONLY TO BE
TAKEN ADVANTAGE OF BY OTHERS.
THE GUNDAM MEISTERS BATTLE
AMIDST SWIRLING CONSPIRACIES.
NEXT EPISODE,
"INTERNATIONAL NEGOTIATION".
POLITICS IS LIKE
A KALEIDOSCOPE,
ALL COLORS SHIFT.