(Boom)
(Blast)
(Weapons blasting)
(Boom)
(Rapid blasting)
(Slash)
(Boom)
(Fire raging)
(Gasping for air)
THAT THING'S A...
THAT THING'S A DEMON!
(Boom)
(Nena laughing)
THIS IS SO MUCH FUN!
(Laughing)
Lockon:
THIS MAKES IT THEIR SEVENTH
ARMED INTERVENTION.
THEY KEEP ATTACKING MILITARY
BASES FOR NO GOOD REASON.
AND THEY'RE
ABSOLUTELY ANNIHILATING THEM.
NOT TO SOUND LIKE
ALLELUJAH,
BUT IT'S AS IF I CAN HEAR
ALL THE EVILS OF THE WORLD.
HEARD ANYTHING
FROM PTOLEMY?
REMAIN ON STANDBY.
THANKS TO THOSE GUYS
OUR OPERATION PLAN
HAS BEEN
COMPLETELY RUINED.
I ASSUME MISS SUMERAGI
IS FURIOUSLY ALTERING
ALL HER MISSION PLANS.
IS THIS THE KIND OF THING
GUNDAMS SHOULD BE DOING?
(Sparks flying)
♪
President Stegmeyer:
SO, IT WAS ITALY
THIS TIME.
AND AGAIN, IT WAS
THE THREE NEW GUNDAMS
THAT PERFORMED
THE ATTACK.
MR. PRESIDENT...THE
INTERVENTIONS OF THE NEW MODELS
ARE CLEARLY DIFFERENT IN NATURE
FROM THE PREVIOUS ONES.
DARING TO COME TOGETHER IN A
LARGE JOINT MILITARY EXERCISE
MUST HAVE BROUGHT DOWN THE
WRATH OF THE GUNDAMS.
Official #2C:
THERE IS NO WAY WE CAN DEAL WITH
CELESTIAL BEING ON OUR OWN.
OBVIOUSLY, WE NEED TO STRENGTHEN
OUR TIES WITH THE OTHER BLOCS.
AND YOU THINK THAT WILL
HELP US DEFEAT THE GUNDAMS?
Official #2A:
WELL THEN WHAT DO
YOU SUGGEST WE DO?
IS THERE NOTHING WE
CAN DO TO STOP THEM?
Peries:
COLONEL...
DO YOU THINK THE GUNDAMS
WILL LAUNCH AN ATTACK ON US
UP HERE AS WELL?
THAT IS A POSSIBILITY.
I'D EXPECT THEM TO CONTINUE
SUCH ACTIONS
IF THEIR GOAL
IS TO DESTROY THE WORLD.
YOU DON'T KNOW ANYTHING
ABOUT THE NEW GUNDAMS?
EVEN YOU, AN OBSERVER?
MY INFORMATION IS LIMITED
ACCORDING TO MY ACCESS
LEVEL AS SET BY VEDA.
THEIR TEAM NAME IS
TRINITY.
THEIR MACHINES ARE
CALLED GUNDAM THRONES.
AND THAT'S AS MUCH AS
I KNOW ABOUT THEM.
THIS IS JUST MY
PERSONAL OPINION...
BUT I THINK THEIR
ACTIONS ARE SOMEWHAT EXTREME.
SO TELL ME THEN,
DO YOU BELIEVE
THAT THE EXISTENCE
OF THE TRINITYS IS ALSO
PART OF OUR ORIGINAL PLAN?
THAT'S A REASONABLE CONCLUSION
GIVEN THE FACTS.
AFTER ALL, THEY ARE IN
POSSESSION
OF MOBILE
WEAPONS CALLED GUNDAMS.
Ian:
ABOUT THOSE THRONES...
THEIR SYSTEMS
AND ARMOR
USE THE SAME TECHNOLOGY
THAT OURS DO.
SO THEY'RE
OF THE SAME TYPE.
BUT THEIR GN DRIVES
ARE DIFFERENT.
THEIR SOLAR REACTORS
ARE DIFFERENT?
WELL, THEY'RE
FUNCTIONALLY IDENTICAL...
BUT THE REACTOR CORE
DOESN'T USE A TD BLANKET.
THUS THE OPERATING TIME OF
THE DRIVE ITSELF IS LIMITED.
Ian:
IN OTHER WORDS, THESE ARE
PSEUDO SOLAR REACTORS.
SO, THIS IS A CASE WHERE
SOMEONE STOLE CELESTIAL BEING'S
TECHNOLOGY AND THEN BUILT
THEIR OWN GUNDAMS?
HOW COULD THAT HAPPEN?
THE BLUEPRINTS FOR THE
SOLAR REACTORS
CAN ONLY BE FOUND
IN VEDA'S DATABANKS.
WHICH MEANS...
ARE YOU SAYING
SOMEONE
ACTUALLY HACKED
THEIR WAY INTO VEDA?
THAT'S IMPOSSIBLE!
CHRIS...
THERE'S NO SUCH THING
AS AN ABSOLUTE.
EVEN IF IT WAS TRUE...
IT TAKES QUITE A LOT OF TIME TO
BUILD A SOLAR REACTOR.
WELL, AT THE VERY LEAST, IT
MEANS WE HAVE A TRAITOR
SOMEWHERE IN THE
ORGANIZATION.
SO IT WOULD SEEM.
(Thinking):
LEVEL THREE CLEAR.
LEVEL FOUR. LEVEL FIVE.
(Gasps)
SOME OF THE DATA FROM LEVEL
SEVEN HAS BEEN ALTERED.
I WONDER WHAT
THIS DATA COVERS...
(Alarm sounds)
I'VE BEEN REJECTED?
BUT IT'S ME! HOW COULD
I BE DENIED ACCESS?
(Tieria thinking):
VEDA... WHAT IS GOING ON HERE?
SO... WHAT DO WE
DO NOW?
LOOK, IF THE WORLD
ACTUALLY THINKS
THAT WE'RE BROTHERS IN
ARMS WITH TEAM TRINITY,
THEN IT WOULD BE DANGEROUS TO
GO ON ANY MISSIONS RIGHT NOW.
WE HAVE TO KEEP
AN EYE ON THEM WHILE WE LEARN
AS MUCH AS WE CAN
ABOUT THEM...
THEN WE CAN
DEVISE A RESPONSE.
SOUNDS LIKE A JOB
FOR WANG LIU MEI.
MISTRESS, THE PTOLEMAOIS
SENT US THE BIOMETRIC DATA
THEY GATHERED
ON THE TRINITY PILOTS...
BUT WE HAVEN'T FOUND ANY
MATCHING INDIVIDUALS.
REDOUBLE YOUR EFFORTS,
PLEASE.
AS YOU WISH, MISTRESS.
THE TRINITYS' METHODS ARE
CERTAINLY RECKLESS...
BUT IF THE WORLD
CHANGES AS A RESULT...
(Whoosh)
(Birds chirping)
Graham:
HOWARD MASON...
HOWARD HAD
NOTHING BUT
THE GREATEST RESPECT
FOR YOU, CAPTAIN.
HE BELIEVED THAT
THE FLAG WAS CHOSEN
TO BE OUR NEXT‐GENERATION
MOBILE SUIT...
BECAUSE OF YOUR
EFFORTS AS A TEST PILOT, SIR.
THE ONLY REASON I ACCEPTED
THE ASSIGNMENT
TO BE THE FLAG'S
TEST PILOT WAS BECAUSE
I THOUGHT IT WAS THE BEST.
AND THEN...IN THAT MOCK
BATTLE DURING TESTING...
THAT WAS AN UNFORTUNATE
ACCIDENT, SIR!
CAPTAIN...HOWARD SAID
SOMETHING TO ME ONCE:
"IT'S THANKS
TO THE CAPTAIN
"THAT I WAS ABLE TO
BECOME A FLAG FIGHTER!
"AND NOW I GET THE CHANCE TO
FLY THE SKIES WITH HIM..."
I SEE.
SOUNDS LIKE HE LOVED
THE FLAG...
EVEN MORE THAN I DID.
(Sighs)
REST EASY, HOWARD MASON,
FOR I SWEAR THIS:
I, GRAHAM AKER,
WILL USE A FLAG
WHEN I FINALLY
DEFEAT THE GUNDAMS!
(Grunts)
(People talking)
SORRY FOR MAKING YOU COME
ALL THE WAY OUT HERE.
WELL, IT'S BETTER
THAN MEETING NEAR THE BASE.
MORE IMPORTANTLY,
WHERE'S MY CASH?
SHOOT.
I HEARD YOU WERE IN THAT BIG
MILITARY EXERCISE...
AND THAT YOU
SAW THOSE NEW GUNDAMS
IN THE TAKLAMAKAN DESERT.
YEAH.
I SAW THEM ALRIGHT.
YOU ONLY SAW THEM?
AND I HAPPENED TO OVERHEAR
ONE OF THE PILOTS TALKING.
YOU HEARD THEM?
YEAH.
I WAS FLYING MY
REALDO WHEN ALL OF A SUDDEN
ONE OF THOSE GUNDAMS
SHOT ME DOWN.
THEN I STUMBLED
ACROSS IT WHILE
I WAS WAITING TO BE
RESCUED.
(Gasps)
(Determined grunt)
(Hatch opens)
(Gasps)
(Yawning)
HARO...NOTIFY
LAGUNA, PLEASE.
YEAH, I GUESS SO!
THE PILOT HAD A HELMET ON
SO I COULDN'T SEE HER FACE...
BUT I COULD TELL IT WAS
A YOUNG GIRL
FROM HER VOICE
AND THE SHAPE OF HER FIGURE.
AND YOU'RE CERTAIN YOU
HEARD HER SAY
THOSE EXACT WORDS,
"NOTIFY LAGUNA"?
I GUESS IT'S POSSIBLE I
MIGHT HAVE MISHEARD HER...
ANYWAY, THAT'S ALL THE
INFORMATION I HAVE.
HAVE YOU TOLD THE
MILITARY ABOUT THIS?
NAW, I NEVER FILED
A REPORT ON IT.
(Gulps)
I FIGURED SOMEONE LIKE YOU
WOULD COME ALONG
AND PAY A PRETTY
PRICE FOR THIS INFO.
IT'S A GOOD STORY...CAN I ASK
YOU TO KEEP IT TO YOURSELF
FOR JUST
A LITTLE BIT LONGER?
MY PAYMENT'S GOING TO NEED
TO BE SWEETENED A BIT.
I'LL HAVE SOME MORE CASH
SENT TO YOU IN A FEW DAYS.
APPRECIATE THAT!
MY DAUGHTER'S BIRTHDAY PARTY IS
GOING TO BE EXTRA SPECIAL NOW!
"NOTIFY LAGUNA..."
LAGUNA? IS THAT A NAME?
SOME KIND OF CODEWORD?
IT'S WORTH LOOKING INTO.
FATHER...
LIKE YOU I'M GOING TO LOOK
FOR THE FACTS,
STRING THEM TOGETHER,
AND THEN GET TO
THE TRUTH.
(Humming)
(Tires squeal loudly)
(Gasps)
(Gunshot)
♪
(Laughing)
CONGRATULATIONS!
I WISH YOU BOTH A
LIFE OF HAPPINESS!
THANK YOU, MRS. HALEVY!
FROM BOTH OF US!
(Laughing)
HELLO THERE, SAJI!
HOW YOU DOING?
Saji:
I'M STILL AT WORK. I AGREED
TO TAKE SOME EXTRA SHIFTS
AND NOW I'M EXHAUSTED.
AND YOU?
IT'S LIKE THE BEST
WEDDING EVER!
THE BRIDE IS
LIKE ABSOLUTELY BEAUTIFUL!
THE FOOD IS OUT
OF THIS WORLD!
AND THEN THERE'S‐‐
HUH? I GOT DISCONNECTED.
AH, IT DOESN'T MATTER.
I'VE ALMOST REACHED
MY SAVINGS GOAL!
(Yawning)
JUST A LITTLE LONGER!
HEY, DELIVERY BOY!
ALRIGHT!
SAJI? SAJI!
AW, WHAT IS THIS?
HMM?
I WONDER IF THOSE
LIGHTS UP THERE ARE...
GUNDAMS!
OH, WOW!
I'VE NEVER SEEN THEM FOR REAL!
Johann:
LAGUNA HAS JUST SENT US OUR
LATEST MISSION.
PROCEED TO
THE TARGET POINT.
Michael:
WHAT, ANOTHER ONE?
I DON'T WANT TO! WE'VE BEEN
WORKING NON‐STOP LATELY!
Johann:
HANG IN THERE. WE'RE DOING
THIS TO ERADICATE WAR.
OH, DARN IT!
HUH?
WHAT'S GOING ON HERE?
WE'RE TOTALLY WORKING OUR
BUTTS OFF...
AND THEY'RE
LAUGHING AND HAVING A PARTY!
YOU GUYS JUST DON'T
GET IT, DO YOU?
I THINK YOUR WORLD
IS ABOUT TO CHANGE.
(Laughing)
HEY, WHAT'S THAT?
HUH?
A MOBILE SUIT?
ISN'T THAT A GUNDAM?
A GUNDAM...
WHAT?
YOU'RE BETTER OFF DEAD.
(Blast)
(Boom)
(Screaming)
(Gasps)
(People coughing)
MY DAD...
MY MOM...
(Gasping)
DAD! MOM!
(Boom)
(Screaming)
NENA, WHAT DO YOU
THINK YOU'RE DOING?
SORRY, I MUST HAVE HIT THE
WRONG SWITCH OR SOMETHING!
YOU'RE PROBABLY JUST TIRED
FROM ALL THESE MISSIONS.
DON'T GO OFF
ON YOUR OWN, NENA.
OKAY!
(Giggles)
♪
(Humming)
TEAM TRINITY LAUNCHED AN
ATTACK ON CIVILIANS?
WHAT WERE THEY THINKING?
MAYBE THEY WERE TARGETING
SOMEBODY WHO WAS GUILTY
OF PROMOTING WAR.
BUT IT DOESN'T LOOK
LIKE THAT'S THE CASE HERE.
THERE'S NOTHING ABOUT IT IN
THE MISSION DATA
TRINITY ENTERED
INTO VEDA.
THEY ATTACKED THOSE PEOPLE
FOR NO REASON AT ALL...
BUT THAT'S JUST...
(Bang)
WHAT THE HELL ARE THOSE BASTARDS
DOING?
ARE THEY PLAYING
GAMES?
AN ATTACK ON CIVILIANS...
BY A GUNDAM.
Student #18A:
TERRORISTS AGAIN?
IT SAYS MOBILE SUITS
WERE INVOLVED...
IT'S PROBABLY
THOSE GUNDAMS.
(Phone ringing)
Operator:
THE NUMBER YOU HAVE
DIALED IS NOT IN SERVICE.
I WONDER WHAT'S GOING ON?
MAYBE HER PARENTS ARE
KEEPING HER FROM ANSWERING.
LOUISE HALEVY, THE FOREIGN
EXCHANGE STUDENT?
YES. SHE HASN'T BEEN TO
SCHOOL IN THREE DAYS.
IS SHE YOUR GIRLFRIEND?
UH, YEAH...
(Laughing)
JUST GIVE ME
A MOMENT.
(Chuckling)
(Gasps)
IS THERE SOMETHING WRONG?
IT LOOKS LIKE MISS HALEVY
WAS INVOLVED IN AN ACCIDENT
IN SPAIN AND HAS BEEN
ADMITTED TO THE HOSPITAL.
WHAT KIND OF ACCIDENT
WAS SHE IN?
I DON'T REALLY KNOW, ALL
WE HAVE IS A NOTIFICATION
OF A LEAVE OF ABSENCE.
PLEASE MISS, I NEED THE
NAME OF THE HOSPITAL!
(Engine running)
HUH?
A SPANISH HOLIDAY RESORT...FROM
STATEMENTS BY SURVIVORS,
IT'S KNOWN THE ATTACK
WAS CARRIED OUT BY A GUNDAM...
(Gasping)
BUT WHY?
(Footsteps echo)
HEY THERE...
WHAT BRINGS YOU OUT HERE
THIS TIME OF NIGHT?
KATAGIRI!
WHAT ARE YOU DOING HERE?
YOU'RE SUPPOSED TO BE
IN A HOSPITAL BED!
WITHOUT ME YOU'D NEVER
BE ABLE TO MAINTAIN THIS
CUSTOM FLAG OF YOURS.
AFTER ALL THESE ARE MACHINES
THAT WERE TUNED BY
THE GREAT
PROFESSOR EIFMAN HIMSELF.
(Cries out)
DON'T PUSH YOURSELF,
OLD FRIEND.
I HAVE TO.
HUH?
JUST LIKE YOU WON'T
COMPROMISE ON SOME THINGS...
THERE ARE SOME THINGS I
WON'T COMPROMISE ON.
(Laughs)
YOU ARE SO
DAMN STUBBORN.
NOT AS MUCH
AS YOU ARE.
Katagiri:
I'VE BEEN THINKING
ABOUT THIS...
THE GUNDAMS ATTACKED OVER FLAG
HEADQUARTERS FOR ONE REASON...
AND THAT WAS TO
GET PROFESSOR EIFMAN.
HOW DO YOU FIGURE?
THE PROFESSOR WAS ON THE VERGE
OF FIGURING OUT
THE TRUE NATURE
OF THE GUNDAMS' ENERGY SYSTEMS
AND THEIR SPECIAL
PARTICLES.
SOMEHOW CELESTIAL BEING MUST
HAVE FOUND OUT ABOUT THIS.
SO THEY KILLED HIM
WHILE MAKING IT
LOOK LIKE AN ARMED INTERVENTION.
HMM.
YOU THINK THERE'S A
SPY IN OUR MILITARY?
IT WOULD BE UNREALISTIC TO
THINK THAT THERE WASN'T ONE.
HMM.
(Alarm Sounding):
DETECTING A POSSIBLE GUNDAM AT
POINT F‐ 3988 OVER IOWA!
THEY'VE SPOTTED A GUNDAM!
THERE'S ONLY ONE POSSIBLE
TARGET AT THAT POINT...
(Gasps)
IRIS CORPORATION'S
MUNITIONS PLANT!
IT CAN'T BE! IT MAY BE A
WEAPONS FACTORY
BUT THE WORKERS
THERE ARE ALL CIVILIANS!
IS MY FLAG
READY FOR LAUNCH?
(Over radio):
THIS IS GRAHAM!
I'M TAKING THE LEAD!
Katagiri:
HEADING OUT ALONE
IS JUST RECKLESS!
SOUNDS REASONABLE, TOO BAD
I'M AN UNREASONABLE MAN!
(Screaming)
(Siren wailing)
(Boom)
HUH?
AN INCOMING MACHINE.
AND IT'S A FAST ONE...
SO IT IS ONE OF THE
NEW ONES!
(Rapid blasting)
HE'S GOOD!
I DON'T CARE HOW MUCH
BETTER YOUR MACHINE IS!
TODAY I AM BEYOND THAT!
I STRIKE LIKE AN
AVENGING ANGEL!
WHAT THE...
THAT'S...IMPOSSIBLE!
(Gasping)
THAT WAS FOR YOU, HOWARD.
SOME PAY BACK.
(Vomiting)
(Gasping)
MY BODY CAN'T TAKE
THIS MANY G'S!
(Waves washing on shore)
Lockon:
SETSUNA!
IT'S TEAM TRINITY.
THEY WENT AND DID IT AGAIN.
DID WHAT?
THEY HIT AN
IRIS CORPORATION FACTORY.
OVER EIGHT HUNDRED PEOPLE
DIED IN THE ATTACK.
(Gasps)
ALL THE WORKERS IN THAT
FACTORY WERE CIVILIANS.
IT'S NO BETTER THAN
INDISCRIMINATE TERRORISM!
(Setsuna running)
HUH?
SETSUNA!
(Sumeragi thinking):
VEDA...
THE QUANTUM COMPUTER
PROCESSING SYSTEM
THAT'S THE BACKBONE
OF OUR OPERATION PLAN.
IN THE OFF‐CHANCE THAT
SOMEONE...
HAS ACTUALLY HACKED VEDA,
WE'RE JUST GOING
TO HAVE TO FIND SOME WAY
TO CONTINUE OUR MISSIONS
WITHOUT IT.
THERE IS
NO WAY WE CAN DO IT.
(Beeping)
HUH?
IT'S FROM BILLY...
(Gasps)
NO, PROFESSOR EIFMAN
WAS KILLED!
AND IT WAS IN AN
ATTACK BY GUNDAMS.
THERE'S A PROBLEM,
MISS SUMERAGI!
WHAT'S THE MATTER?
LOUISE WAS HURT?
AND HE'S GOING TO
SPAIN TO BE WITH HER?
SAJI...
(Car zooms by)
(Screeches to a halt)
(Panting)
HEY, YOU!
NO RUNNING IN THE HALLWAY!
(Saji panting)
(Catching breath)
LOUISE?
SAJI... WHY ARE YOU HERE?
(Sighs)
I HEARD YOU
WERE IN AN ACCIDENT.
SORRY IT TOOK ME SO
LONG TO GET HERE.
BUT YOU'RE
SKIPPING SCHOOL.
AW, DON'T WORRY.
BUT WHAT A RELIEF...
YOU SEEM WELL.
THANK GOD FOR THAT.
OH, THAT'S RIGHT! I'VE GOT
SOMETHING FOR YOU, LOUISE...
IT'S RIGHT HERE...
WHAT'S THAT?
(Gasps)
FOR ME?
(Chuckling)
IT'S THAT SET OF RINGS YOU
WANTED A WHILE BACK!
I WORKED LIKE CRAZY DURING
THE WHOLE EXAM BREAK...
AND I MADE
ENOUGH TO BUY THEM!
THEY'RE FOR YOU...
LOUISE!
IT'S BEAUTIFUL...
(Nervous chuckle)
UH LOUISE...I HAVE SOMETHING
I HAVE TO TELL YOU...
SEE, THE MORE I
THINK OF YOU‐‐
I'M SO... SORRY.
HUH?
YOU WENT TO THE TROUBLE
OF BUYING THESE...
AND THEY'RE SO
BEAUTIFUL...
BUT I CAN'T
WEAR THIS RING.
UH...
I CAN'T WEAR THIS RING.
(Gasps)
OH, NO, LOUISE...
YOU MEAN...
(Sobbing)
I REALLY AM...
SORRY.
(Weeping)
(Gasps)
Nurse:
LOUISE'S PARENTS, ALONG
WITH ALL OF HER RELATIVES,
WERE LOST
IN THE ACCIDENT.
DON'T UPSET HER.
Nurse #18C:
I KNOW THEY WANT TO ELIMINATE
WAR OR SOMETHING LIKE THAT,
BUT WHEN THEY
FIGHT PEOPLE GET HURT.
WE'LL DO OUR BEST TO
HEAL THEIR INJURIES...
BUT WE CAN'T
HEAL THEIR HEARTS.
Nurse #18D:
WHAT? BUT THE HALEVYS
WERE RICH AND FAMOUS!
Nurse #18E:
THE FAMILY WAS
ATTACKED BY A GUNDAM!
THE WHOLE FAMILY'S GONE!
Nurse #18F:
HOW AWFUL...
Nurse #18G:
MAYBE THE FAMILY WAS
PROMOTING WAR...
Nurse #18F:
BUT THEY WERE CIVILIANS!
Nurse #18E:
IN THE END, IT JUST
MEANS MORE WORK FOR US.
(Sighs)
(Sobs)
OH, LOUISE...
(Weeping)
Michael:
I NEVER THOUGHT THERE
WAS SOMEBODY OUT THERE
WHO COULD ACTUALLY
GIVE YOU TROUBLE.
Nena:
CARELESSNESS
IS THE REAL ENEMY.
I'M JUST GOING TO HAVE TO
TAKE THAT TO HEART.
HUH?
WHAT THE...
THOSE ARE PARTICLE BEAMS!
(Grunting)
A GUNDAM!
Johann:
IT'S THE GUNDAM EXIA!
EXIA HAS LOCATED THE TARGETS.
HAVE CONCLUDED THE THREE
GUNDAM THRONE UNITS
ARE GUILTY
OF PROMOTING CONFLICT.
COMMENCING ARMED
INTERVENTION.
EXIA...
WILL ELIMINATE TARGETS!
♪
Narrator:
THE ONE HE WISHED
VENGEANCE UPON
WAS RIGHT THERE
BESIDE HIM.
WHEN HE LEARNS THIS,
LOCKON GATHERS HIS ANGER
AND AIMS HIS WEAPON.
NEXT EPISODE:
"BONDS".
WHO IS THE ONE HE SHOULD
BE TARGETING?