(Cameras snap)
TARIBIA RETURNS TO
THE UNION,
AND THE AMERICAN PRESIDENT
MAKES AN EMERGENCY VISIT.
HE PROMISES
MORE MATERIAL AID
AND AN INCREASE IN THEIR
ENERGY SUPPLY.
IT LOOKS LIKE THIS WAS
ALL COOKED UP
BY AMERICA AND TARIBIA.
THAT MEANS CELESTIAL BEING
WAS BEING USED
AS A TOOL ALL ALONG.
NO, NOT EXACTLY.
CELESTIAL BEING WAS JUST
FOLLOWING ITS MANDATE
TO ELIMINATE WAR.
LEADING IT TO
ATTACK TARIBIA.
EVEN IF IT WENT
AGAINST WORLD OPINION.
IT MIGHT NOT BE SO WISE
TO TRY USING THEM
FOR OUR PURPOSES,
AFTER ALL.
I SEE.
IT'S ALMOST TIME FOR
YOUR INTERNATIONAL
TOUR, PRINCESS.
I'M ANTICIPATING
GOOD RESULTS.
I KNOW YOU ARE,
AND I PROMISE I'LL TRY
TO DO MY BEST.
TO SAVE AZADISTAN,
WE NEED TO HAVE ACCESS
TO SOLAR ENERGY.
MAY I ASK YOU ONE
THING, PRINCESS?
WHY EXACTLY DID
YOU ACCEPT THIS ROLE?
I HAD NO CHOICE.
BECAUSE ONLY I CAN DO IT.
♪
Announcer:
GOOD DAY AND
THANK YOU FOR USING
HEAVEN'S PILLAR TRAVEL
BUREAU...
Saji:
AW, SIS. YOU DIDN'T HAVE
TO COME SEE ME OFF.
I HAD SOME BUSINESS
TO TAKE CARE OF HERE.
NOW LISTEN, SAJI,
STUDY HARD WHEN YOU'RE
UP THERE.
YOUR SCHOLARSHIP IS
TAKING CARE OF YOUR STUDY TOUR,
BUT I'M THE ONE PAYING
FOR YOUR TICKET.
YEAH, I'M SORRY
FOR ALL THE TROUBLE.
BUT LOUISE INSISTED
ON GETTING A PRIVATE CAR.
AUGH!
LITTLE RICH GIRLS CAN
BE JUST SO‐‐
ARE YOU GUYS TALKING
ABOUT ME?
LOUISE...
PLEASE, DON'T WORRY
ABOUT A THING, KINUE!
SAJI NEEDS SOMEONE TO
TAKE CARE OF HIM
AND BELIEVE ME,
I'M MORE THAN CAPABLE!
UH, OKAY. I GUESS I CAN
RELAX IF LOUISE IS THERE.
BUT THIS ISN'T SOME KIND
OF VACATION
SO IT DOESN'T MEAN
YOU CAN TAKE IT EASY.
AND NO FUNNY STUFF
WITH LOUISE, GOT IT?
JUST WHAT ARE YOU
IMPLYING, SIS?!
(Laughing)
OH, THERE'S NOTHING
TO WORRY ABOUT THERE!
SAJI WOULDN'T KNOW HOW TO,
EVEN IF HE WANTED!
UH...REALLY?
HONESTLY,
I'M STARTING TO WONDER
IF SHE'S THE RIGHT GIRL
FOR YOU!
HEY KINUE, I CAN HEAR YOU.
(Chuckles)
ALRIGHT,
THE PAPERWORK'S DONE.
LET'S GO,
LIEUTENANT.
ROGER THAT, COLONEL.
AN EXPERIMENTAL
MOBILE SUIT TEST.
Allelujah:
THE MISSION PLAN JUST
ARRIVED FROM MISS SUMERAGI.
WE'LL OBSERVE
THE PERFORMANCE
OF AN EXPERIMENTAL
MOBILE SUIT.
DEPENDING ON THE SITUATION,
WE MAY EVEN HAVE TO DESTROY IT.
YOU NEED TO BE CAREFUL
WHEN YOU'RE OUT THERE,
ALLELUJAH.
EVER SINCE THAT
AFFAIR IN TARIBIA,
THE WORLD HAS BECOME
A LITTLE LESS
FRIENDLY TO US.
YEAH, THANKS.
I'LL BE SURE TO
WATCH OUT.
Announcer:
GOOD DAY AND THANK YOU
FOR USING HEAVEN'S PILLAR
TRAVEL BUREAU
NUMBER E‐603 TODAY.
THIS LINEAR TRAIN
IS A DIRECT,
NON‐STOP ASCENT TO
THE LOW ORBITAL STATION
TRUE PILLAR.
WE WILL BE
ARRIVING AT 18:32.
09:32 OF THE FOLLOWING DAY,
GREENWICH MEAN TIME.
WE HAVE NOW COMPLETED OUR
INITIAL ACCELERATION.
FROM THIS POINT ON,
THE TRAIN WILL BE IN
A GENTLE DECELERATION STAGE.
THE CAR INTERIOR
WILL EXPERIENCE
A QUASI‐WEIGHTLESS
ENVIRONMENT.
PLEASE USE CAUTION WHEN
UNFASTENING YOUR SEATBELTS.
THE SOLAR POWER ARRAY
CONSTRUCTION PROJECT.
AN UNDERTAKING WHICH BEGAN
FIFTY YEARS AGO,
INITIATED WHEN EARTH'S
FOSSIL FUELS WERE EXHAUSTED
AND HUMANITY BEGAN THE SEARCH
FOR A NEW SOURCE OF ENERGY.
(Humming)
HUH?
THE ARRAY CONSISTS OF ROUGHLY
30,000 POWER GENERATION
SATELLITES PLACED IN...
WHOA!
YOU KNOW, I DON'T BELIEVE
I EVER ASKED YOU
WHY YOU VOLUNTEERED
TO JOIN
THE SUPER‐HUMAN
INSTITUTE.
I DIDN'T VOLUNTEER.
IN FACT,
I AM A DESIGNER BABY
CREATED SPECIFICALLY FOR
THE SUPER‐SOLDIER PROGRAM.
NUMBER ONE HAS NANO‐MACHINES
EMBEDDED IN HER
TO MAINTAIN
HER PHYSICAL FUNCTIONS.
THIS ALLOWS HER TO REMAIN
ACTIVE IN SPACE
FOR EXTENDED PERIODS.
IN ADDITION, THE SENSORY
AMPLIFICATION TREATMENT
WE APPLIED
TO HER NERVOUS‐‐
THAT'S ENOUGH!
IS THERE SOMETHING
BOTHERING YOU ABOUT THIS?
YOU PEOPLE DON'T SEE
ANYTHING WRONG
WITH WHAT YOU'RE DOING
IN YOUR
SECRET LABORATORIES?
NO, NOT AT ALL.
IF WE'RE TO ADJUST TO
THE HARSH ENVIRONMENT OF SPACE,
THE LIEUTENANT HERE
IS AN ABSOLUTE NECESSITY.
SOMETHING WRONG...COLONEL?
HUH?
NO.
Announcer:
THE SATELLITES,
CHARGED WITH SOLAR ENERGY,
TRANSMIT THE POWER TO THE
ORBITAL ELEVATOR VIA MICROWAVE.
AND THROUGH THE ELEVATOR,
IT IS SUBSEQUENTLY
DISTRIBUTED
TO VARIOUS
REGIONS ON THE SURFACE.
(Humming)
OVER 1.2 EXAJOULES OF POWER
ARE COLLECTED
AND TRANSFERRED IN
A SINGLE DAY.
CURRENTLY,
DISTRIBUTION OF POWER
TO THE THIRTY‐FIVE NATIONS OF
THE HUMAN REFORM LEAGUE
(Giggles)
IS ACHIEVED THROUGH
THE USE OF ENERGY TUBES AND...
LOUISE,
I WAS WATCHING THAT!
NEVER MIND THAT.
WE'RE GOING TO GO OUT
AND PLAY!
♪
AND HERE WE ARE AT LAST!
(Sighs)
WHAT'S WRONG?
I'M KIND OF TIRED.
YOU'VE BEEN DRAGGING ME
EVERYWHERE NON‐STOP.
YOU'RE SO OUT
OF SHAPE.
YOU'RE JUST OUT OF
CONTROL, LOUISE!
AH, YOU TWO MUST BE SAJI
CROSSROAD AND LOUISE HALEVY!
AH, YES!
THAT'S US!
I'M BORS ASSAN
AND I'LL BE SUPERVISING
YOUR TRAINING.
WELCOME TO THE LOW ORBITAL
STATION TRUE PILLAR!
Bors:
SAJI, DO YOU KNOW WHY THE LOW
ORBITAL RING IS NECESSARY?
Saji:
YEAH, FORCING A MAGNETIC
FLUID THROUGH THE RING
CREATES THE
CENTRIFUGAL FORCE NEEDED
TO MAINTAIN THE STATION'S
ORBITAL ALTITUDE, RIGHT?
I SEE SOMEONE'S
DONE HIS HOMEWORK!
Louise:
HEY, SAJI!
COME LOOK AT THIS!
LOUISE,
YOU SHOULDN'T BE THERE!
THIS AREA IS OUT OF BOUNDS!
HUH?
BEAUTIFUL.
YEAH, IT SURE IS.
THIS IS WAY DIFFERENT
THAN A PICTURE.
YEAH.
BE CAREFUL, YOU TWO.
THERE'S STILL A LITTLE GRAVITY
AT TEN THOUSAND KILOMETERS.
ONE WRONG STEP AND
YOU'LL END UP FALLING
ALL THE WAY BACK TO EARTH.
AH, RIGHT SIR!
WE'RE SORRY!
(Screams)
(Grunts)
(Grunting)
(Screams)
SAJI, YOU IDIOT!
YOU'VE GOT TO SAVE ME PROPERLY!
(Louise screaming)
OH, BOY.
COLONEL, THIS WAY,
PLEASE.
SO THIS IS THE ONE?
YES, SIR.
A MACHINE
ADAPTED TO
SUPER SOLDIER NUMBER ONE'S
REACTION SPEED.
THE M. S. J. 06II‐SP,
TIEREN TAOZI.
THIS WILL BE MY MOBILE SUIT.
OUR ACE IN THE HOLE AGAINST
THE GUNDAMS.
EXCUSE ME, SIR,
HAVE YOU FINISHED YOUR MEAL?
THANKS.
AND WOULD YOU CARE
FOR ANYTHING TO DRINK?
COFFEE'S FINE.
CERTAINLY SIR.
ARE YOU ON VACATION?
I MUCH PREFER
THE WAY
THE EARTH LOOKS
FROM UP IN SPACE.
I KNOW EXACTLY WHAT
YOU MEAN.
THE SURFACE
CAN BE SO COMPLICATED.
AND IT'S ONLY
GOTTEN WORSE
WITH THIS
CELESTIAL BEING GROUP.
INDEED.
THEY ARE A PAIN.
WE'LL BE ARRIVING
SHORTLY, SIR.
UNTIL THEN,
MAKE YOURSELF COMFORTABLE.
WALKING IN GRAVITY
AGAIN IS REALLY GREAT!
THAT'S FOR SURE! HMM?
MISTRESS,
IT IS ALMOST TIME.
YES. I AM AWARE OF THAT.
HMM...
HUH?
YEOW!
EYES FORWARD,
MISTER!
I‐I'M SORRY.
Sergei:
LIEUTENANT, LET'S CHECK OUT
YOUR MACHINE'S MANEUVERABILITY.
FOLLOW THE DESIGNATED COURSE
AT FULL ACCELERATION.
Peries:
ROGER THAT, COLONEL.
HERE I GO.
I AM NOW AT
FULL ACCELERATION.
A COURSE ERROR OF ONLY 0.25
AT MAXIMUM ACCELERATION.
IS THIS WHAT
A SUPER SOLDIER CAN DO?
Sergei:
BUT SHE'S STILL
JUST A CHILD, REALLY.
(Gasps)
WHAT IS THIS FEELING?
(Grunts)
WHAT IS THIS?
MY HEAD!
IT HURTS!
Sergei:
LIEUTENANT!
YOU'RE VEERING OFF
THE DESIGNATED COURSE.
WHAT'S WRONG?
C‐COLONEL SOMETHING'S...
THROBBING...IN MY HEAD.
(Groaning)
WHERE DID THIS
HEADACHE COME FROM?!
(Groaning)
DAMN!
WHAT THE HELL IS THIS,
AND JUST WHO IS SCREWING
AROUND WITH MY HEAD?!
WHO ARE YOU?!
I AM GOING TO
KILL YOU!
N‐NO...!
Sergei:
LIEUTENANT! STOP!
NO! STOP!
NO...!
STOP IT! LIEUTENANT!
Peries:
NO!
GET OUT! STOP IT!
Sergei:
LIEUTENANT!
NO!
LIEUTENANT, CEASE FIRE!
(Peries screaming)
(Boom)
WHAT'S THAT?
MAYBE THERE'S
SOME DEBRIS HITTING US.
NO!
THAT'S ENOUGH,
LIEUTENANT! STOP!
(Creaking)
(Screaming)
WHAT IS GOING
ON HERE?
(Alarm ringing)
LOUISE!
WHAT'S HAPPENING?
THE GRAVITY'S GONE.
WHO IS IT?
WHO IS THAT PERSON?
HEY, LOOK!
ISN'T THAT
A GRAVITY BLOCK?
AN ACCIDENT?
IT SURE SUCKS TO BE THEM.
HALLELUJAH.
YOU STAY OUT OF THIS.
HALLELUJAH!
Boy:
ARE WE... GOING TO DIE?
OH, NO!
I DON'T WANT TO DIE!
PLEASE, KILL ME...
ALLELUJAH.
NOT AGAIN, NOT AGAIN!
Sergei:
LIEUTENANT,
THIS IS A DISASTER.
LIEUTENANT!
CONTROL ROOM,
THIS IS SERGEI.
GIVE ME A DAMAGE REPORT ON
THE GRAVITY BLOCKS.
HERE'S THE SITUATION
COLONEL.
GRAVITY BLOCK
NUMBER SEVEN IS DRIFTING.
AND ACCORDING TO THE
DISTRESS SIGNAL WE RECEIVED,
THERE ARE 232 PEOPLE
STRANDED INSIDE IT.
WHAT ABOUT A RESCUE TEAM?
ONE IS SUPPOSED TO DEPLOY
IN SEVEN MINUTES.
AND WE'RE SCRAMBLING
A SMALL COMBAT TEAM
TO ESCORT THEM AS WELL.
HOWEVER, BECAUSE
OF THE EXPLOSIVE SHOCK
AND AN AIR LEAK,
GRAVITY BLOCK NUMBER SEVEN
IS LOSING VELOCITY!
IT'LL BE DRAGGED INTO
THE EARTH'S GRAVITATIONAL FIELD
IN FOURTEEN MINUTES!
WHAT?!
Sergei:
I'LL START THE RESCUE!
DEPLOY A RECOVERY TEAM
FOR THE LIEUTENANT'S MACHINE.
BUT, SIR, AN OBJECT
WITH THAT MUCH MASS‐‐
LIVES ARE AT
STAKE HERE!
Liu‐Mei:
THEY'RE SENDING A RESCUE TEAM.
PROBLEM IS...
THERE'S JUST NO WAY
IT'LL MAKE IT IN TIME.
EARTH'S GRAVITY IS GOING
TO SEIZE
THE GRAVITY BLOCK
AND THEN PULL IT IN.
MISTRESS!
EXCUSE ME,
BUT IT'S
ALLELUJAH HAPTISM.
WHAT?
Saji:
THIS ENTIRE BLOCK
HAS BEEN DETACHED FROM
THE STATION!
HOLD ON, DOES THAT
MEAN WE'RE ADRIFT?
NO WAY.
A RESCUE TEAM IS
ON ITS WAY.
WE JUST HAVE
TO BE PATIENT.
Sergei:
SEVEN MINUTES UNTIL
THE ESCAPE LIMIT ZONE.
TO BRING
THE SPEED OF THE BLOCK
UP TO ORBITAL VELOCITY...
I'LL HAVE TO ACCELERATE THAT
ENORMOUS STRUCTURE!
(Clang)
(Gasps)
WHAT'S THAT?!
(Grunting)
SOMETHING'S WRONG!
I JUST CALCULATED IT
ON MY TERMINAL!
THIS BLOCK IS
GOING TO BE TRAPPED
IN THE EARTH'S
GRAVITATIONAL FIELD
IN ABOUT IN FIVE MINUTES!
WHAT DID YOU
JUST SAY?!
SAJI...
IS THAT GUY SERIOUS?
IN FIVE MINUTES
WE'RE GOING TO START...
BLOCK NUMBER SEVEN SIMPLY
HAS TOO MUCH MASS.
MY MACHINE
DOESN'T HAVE ENOUGH THRUST!
TWO HUNDRED SECONDS UNTIL
THE ESCAPE LIMIT ZONE.
AND AT THIS RATE,
MY MACHINE'S
GOING TO BE CAUGHT
IN THE GRAVITATIONAL FIELD
AS WELL.
AM I GOING TO HAVE TO
ABANDON THEM?
OVER TWO HUNDRED PEOPLE!
WHY?! WHY DOES SPACE
HAVE TO BE SO MERCILESS?!
(Beeping)
WHAT KIND OF MACHINE
CAN APPROACH THIS FAST?
WHY DIDN'T IT SHOW
ON MY RADAR?
IS THAT A...?
A GUNDAM?
Liu‐Mei:
ALLELUJAH,
ALLELUJAH HAPTISM!
WHAT ARE YOU DOING?
YOUR MISSION HAS GOT NOTHING
TO DO WITH THIS.
YOU COULD NEVER UNDERSTAND...
THE FEELINGS OF SOMEONE WHO
IS ADRIFT IN SPACE.
TWENTY SECONDS TILL
THE ESCAPE LIMIT ZONE!
KYRIOS!
WHAT THE HELL?!
HUH, AGAIN?!
GO...!
IT‐IT'S STOPPED FALLING!
BUT, WHY IS CELESTIAL BEING
DOING RESCUE WORK?
NOW IT'S ALL UP
TO MISS SUMERAGI.
Christina:
WE JUST GOT AN URGENT CODED
TRANSMISSION FROM WANG LIU‐MEI.
HE'S DOING RESCUE WORK?
WHAT IS THAT
BOY THINKING?
SO, WHAT DO WE DO?
WHAT ELSE CAN WE DO?!
Journalist:
IT'S COMING IN!
A MISSING PERSONS LIST FROM
THE STATION ACCIDENT !
(Concerned chatter)
(Gasps)
NO WAY.
Sergei:
EVEN WITH THE GUNDAM'S THRUST,
THE BEST WE CAN DO IS
TO JUST MAINTAIN
OUR CURRENT POSITION.
AND THEN, WE'LL START TO
FALL WHEN WE RUN OUT OF ENERGY.
Allelujah:
CAN YOU HEAR ME?
EVERYONE, MOVE TO THE
CENTRAL BLOCK!
Sergei:
IS THAT THE GUNDAM
PILOT SPEAKING?
Allelujah:
I REPEAT, IF YOU DON'T
WANT TO DIE,
MOVE TO THE CENTER!
IS SOMEONE TRYING
TO RESCUE US?
COME ON LOUISE,
LET'S GO!
THERE'S NO TIME!
HURRY UP!
HIS VOICE... HE'S A YOUNG MAN.
HEY, SAJI...
THERE'S A CHANCE YOU AND
I MIGHT DIE OUT HERE.
I JUST WANT
TO SAY SOMETHING.
LOUISE...
Sergei:
COME IN, GUNDAM PILOT!
THIS BLOCK IS ABOUT TO
ENTER THE ESCAPE LIMIT ZONE.
THIS IS THE END. GET AWAY!
(Allelujah scoffs)
I CAN'T DO THAT!
FAILURE IS NOT
AN OPTION.
NOT FOR CELESTIAL BEING.
BESIDES...
LOOK, SAJI,
I JUST WANT TO SAY...
A GUNDAM MEISTER
IS NEVER ALONE!
(Blast)
WHAT THE...?
NICELY DONE...
Allelujah:
LOCKON STRATOS.
G. N. PARTICLE COMPRESSION
IN PROGRESS.
CHARGING COMPLETE IN
TWENTY, NINETEEN, EIGHTEEN,
SEVENTEEN, SIXTEEN,
FIFTEEN...
CLOUDS ARE MOVING
IN AND BLOCKING MY SHOT.
TEAR THEM UP, SETSUNA!
ROGER THAT.
(Grunts)
Haro:
CHARGING COMPLETE!
TARGETED AND FIRING!
(Boom)
SOME NICE SUPPORT,
MISS SUMERAGI.
NOW, MOVE!
THEY TARGETED THE TWO BLOCKS
FROM THE GROUND
AND CUT THEM OFF.
THIS REDUCED
THE TOTAL MASS
SO THEY COULD PUSH IT
TO A STABLE ORBIT.
(Beep)
HUH?
Sergei:
THE RESCUE TEAM'S HERE.
Soldier:
C‐COLONEL,
IT'S THE GUNDAM!
THE RESCUE WORK TAKES
PRIORITY!
R‐ROGER!
I AM NOT SO CALLOUS AS TO BE
UNGRATEFUL FOR THEIR HELP.
Journalist:
THIS JUST IN!
ALL THE PEOPLE WHO
WERE IN DANGER WERE RESCUED!
(Cheering)
(Gasps)
(Sighs)
MISSION COMPLETE!
HUH?
WE ABANDONED THE MISSION
THAT VEDA RECOMMENDED
AND MADE A RESCUE OPERATION
OUR PRIORITY.
ON TOP OF THAT,
WE SHOWED THE WHOLE WORLD
DYNAMES' HIGH ALTITUDE
FIRING CAPABILITY.
SO, WE'LL HAVE TO
COMPLETELY REVISE OUR PLANS,
WON'T WE?
YOU CHANGED THE MISSION,
AND YOU'RE THE ONE WHO GAVE
LOCKON STRATOS HIS ORDERS.
I DIDN'T CHANGE THE MISSION
TO HELP ALLELUJAH HAPTISM.
I PROTECTED THE GUNDAM.
SOMEONE WITH HIS
TEMPERAMENT...
SHOULD NOT BE
PILOTING A GUNDAM.
AND WHAT OF
YOUR TEMPERAMENT?
Louise:
YOU AND I,
WE WERE PRETTY CLOSE TO
DYING WEREN'T WE?
IT'S OKAY!
IT WAS SO UNREAL.
BUT I'M GLAD IT'S OVER!
HEY, LOUISE,
YOU WERE GOING TO TELL ME
SOMETHING EARLIER.
WHAT WAS IT?
OH...
GO AHEAD.
UH...
NO, NOT NOW.
♪
Narrator:
EVEN IF IT'S A SET‐UP BATTLE,
CELESTIAL BEING CANNOT
STAY SILENT.
A GUNDAM WITH
NEW EQUIPMENT REVEALS
ITS EXISTENCE TO THE WORLD.
NEXT EPISODE,
"THE SEVEN SWORDS".
THERE'S NO TURNING BACK.