(Machine gun firing)
Al‐Saachez:
THIS BATTLE...IS A HOLY WAR
IN THE NAME OF GOD.
(Grunts)
WE SHALL STRIKE DOWN
THE INFIDELS
WHO DISRESPECT OUR TRADITIONS
AND LAY WASTE
TO THE LAND OF GOD.
(Tank running)
(Panting)
WE MUST NOT SUBMIT
TO THE INFIDELS.
(Gun shots firing)
(Tank explodes)
(Gasps)
(Panting)
(Screams)
BY DYING IN BATTLE...
WE SHALL BE LED
INTO THE PRESENCE OF GOD.
(Breathing heavily)
(Setsuna thinking)
IN THIS WORLD...
THERE IS NO GOD.
(Gun shots blast)
(Gasps)
Al‐Saachez:
THIS BATTLE IS A HOLY WAR...
(Thinking)
IN THIS WORLD
THERE IS NO GOD.
Al‐Saachez:
WE SHALL STRIKE DOWN
THE INFIDELS
WHO DISRESPECT OUR TRADITIONS
AND LAY WASTE
TO THE LAND OF GOD.
(Panting)
(Gun shots firing)
(Gun shot blasts)
HUH?
(Grunts)
(Gasps)
♪
(Gun shots firing)
(Firing continues)
(Audience in awe)
SO THIS IS THE ENACT.
THE FIRST A. E. U. MOBILE SUIT
THAT RUNS ON SOLAR ENERGY.
THE DEVELOPMENT
OF THE A. E. U.'S
ORBITAL ELEVATOR
IS DEFINITELY LAGGING.
THEY PROBABLY WANT TO
MAKE UP FOR THAT
BY MAKING THEIR
MOBILE SUITS STATE OF THE ART.
WELL, LOOK AT THIS.
SHOULD THE ACE OF MSWAD BE
SHOWING HIS FACE HERE?
OF COURSE
I SHOULDN'T BE HERE.
YOU KNOW, THE A. E. U.'S
GOT SOME NERVE, ALRIGHT.
ANNOUNCING THEIR NEW MODEL
AT THE SAME TIME
AS THE HUMAN REFORM LEAGUE'S
TENTH ANNIVERSARY CEREMONY.
SO, WHAT DO YOU THINK
OF THIS MACHINE ANYWAY?
TO BE PERFECTLY
HONEST,
IT'S JUST A KNOCKOFF
OF OUR FLAG MODEL.
ONLY THE EXTERIOR DESIGN
IS ORIGINAL.
Patrick:
YOU THERE!
I CAN HEAR YOU!
WHAT DID YOU JUST SAY?
WELL? COME ON!!
WELL, AT LEAST IT HAS
GOOD SOUND PICKUP.
I GUESS SO!
2‐4‐0‐0‐8‐2 EXIA HAS
TARGET LOCATION IN SIGHT.
CEASE G. N. PARTICLE DISPERSAL
UPON ARRIVAL AT TARGET.
TARGET CONFIRMED.
COMMENCING
FIRST PHASE ON SCHEDULE.
CAPTAIN! I'VE SPOTTED
AN INCOMING SILHOUETTE!
WHAT?
IT'S AT
THREE O'CLOCK, SIR!
WHICH SQUADRON?
THIS IS AN EXERCISE
DAMNIT.
WARN THEM OFF!
IT'S NOT SHOWING UP
ON OUR RADAR!
NOTHING HERE, SIR!
GET A VISUAL ON IT!
(Gasps)
JUST WHAT KIND OF
UNIT IS THAT?
IT'S BEGUN.
WHAT?
AN UNKNOWN?
WHY NOW OF ALL TIMES?!
(Groans)
HUH?
A MOBILE SUIT.
INCREDIBLE.
I DIDN'T KNOW
THEY HAD ANOTHER NEW MODEL.
THEN IT'S NOT THEIRS.
WHAT IS WITH THAT LIGHT?
(Crowd gasps)
ENACT!
CAN YOU HEAR ME, ENACT?!
PATRICK! DAMN!
I CAN'T GET THROUGH.
WHAT'S GOING ON HERE?
COMMUNICATIONS
ARE OUT?
Security Officer:
EVERYONE, WE'VE
BEEN ADVISED TO EVACUATE!
IT'S NOT
AN A. E. U. MACHINE?
WELL, WHOSE IS IT?
ALRIGHT,
WHO THE HELL ARE YOU?
FROM THE UNION?
HUMAN REFORM LEAGUE?
WELL, EITHER WAY,
YOU'RE A PARTY‐CRASHER
AND YOU WEREN'T INVITED.
AND NOW YOU'RE
GOING TO PAY THE PRICE!
WHAT THE HELL IS THAT IDIOT
DOING OUT THERE?
DOESN'T HE KNOW
HOW MUCH MONEY IT COST
TO DEVELOP THAT THING?
IT'S A GOOD
OPPORTUNITY.
IT'LL JUST RAISE
THE VALUE OF THE ENACT.
AFTER ALL,
PATRICK COLASOUR
IS OUR MILITARY'S
TOP ACE, RIGHT?
HIS PERSONALITY COULD USE
A LITTLE WORK, THOUGH.
HEY, YOU!
DO YOU HAVE ANY IDEA
WHO YOU'RE MESSING WITH HERE?
I'M PATRICK COLASOUR
OF THE A. E. U.!
I'VE NEVER LOST A MOCK BATTLE
BECAUSE I'M
JUST THAT SPECIAL!
SO DON'T SAY I DIDN'T
WARN YOU!
(Crowd groans)
THAT IDIOT!
Patrick:
WELL, COME ON!
EXIA, READY FOR
TARGET ELIMINATION.
(Slash)
WHAT THE HELL?!
(Crash)
AH! YOU BASTARD!
YOU DON'T GET IT,
DO YOU?!
Patrick:
I'M... SPECIAL!
I'VE DONE
TWO THOUSAND...
OF THESE MOCK BATTLES!
HMM?
EXCUSE ME!
HEY, WHAT THE...?
I SAID, "EXCUSE ME."
Graham:
GUN... DAM...
IS THAT THE NAME OF THE MOBILE
SUIT OR SOMETHING ELSE?
A GUNDAM?
EXIA, FIRST PHASE COMPLETE.
NOW PROCEEDING TO
SECOND PHASE.
AGAIN WITH THAT
LIGHT.
HOW CAN IT FLY WITHOUT
A PROPULSION SYSTEM?
WHERE IS HE?!
WHERE'D HE GO?!
MY NAME IS
PATRICK COLASOUR AND...
HUH, THAT'S
PRETTY IMPRESSIVE.
I GUESS
THE BRAND NEW ENACT
DESERVES HIGH MARKS
FOR PILOT SAFETY.
BUT THAT MOBILE SUIT IS
A WHOLE OTHER THING.
WAS THIS MEANT TO HAMPER
THE A. E. U.'S MILITARY BUILDUP?
OR MAYBE, IT'S JUST
MEANT TO BE A WARNING.
WHATEVER THE CASE,
THERE'S NO WAY
THE A. E. U. IS GOING TO TAKE
SOMETHING LIKE THIS LYING DOWN.
(Plane engine running)
Christina:
PTOLEMY PERIMETER DENSITY,
MAINTAINING MISSION MODE.
EXIA HAS PASSED THE SCHEDULED
OPERATION TIME
FOR FIRST PHASE.
IT IS MOST LIKELY
IN THE SECOND PHASE NOW.
I WONDER IF SETSUNA'S
DOING ALL RIGHT OUT THERE?
WELL, IF HE ISN'T,
THEN THAT SPELLS
THE END OF CELESTIAL BEING,
DOESN'T IT?
THAT'S ENOUGH
IDLE CHATTER YOU TWO.
IT'S ALMOST TIME TO
COMMENCE THE THIRD PHASE.
I DON'T KNOW WHY
YOU HAVE TO BE SO UPTIGHT.
AFTER ALL THIS IS
CELESTIAL BEING'S BIG DEBUT!
LET'S DO IT WITH FLAIR!
HEY!
ARE YOU DRINKING?!
DID I HEAR THAT
RIGHT?
WELL, WHY NOT?
I'M JUST IN CHARGE
OF PLANNING THE MISSIONS.
THE REST IS UP TO YOU GUYS.
(Gulping)
Feldt:
CONTAINER LOADING COMPLETED.
MOVING KYRIOS TO
CATAPULT DECK.
A REAL BATTLE, HALLELUJAH.
JUST WHAT YOU WANTED.
(Sighs)
BUT THIS IS DEPRESSING TO ME.
Feldt:
KYRIOS ON CATAPULT DECK.
INCREASING LINEAR CATAPULT
VOLTAGE FROM 230 TO 520.
KYRIOS STABILIZED WITH
LINEAR FIELD.
LAUNCH PREPARATIONS COMPLETE.
TRANSFERRING TIMING CONTROL
TO KYRIOS.
ROGER,
I HAVE CONTROL.
KYRIOS, NOW COMMENCING
OPERATION.
(Blast)
Reporter:
ORBITAL ELEVATOR NUMBER TWO,
BETTER KNOWN
AS "HEAVEN'S PILLAR".
HERE ON THE GEOSTATIONARY
ORBITAL STATION,
A FESTIVE
PARTY IS UNDERWAY
CELEBRATING THE TENTH
ANNIVERSARY OF THE STATION'S
VERY FIRST
ELECTRICITY TRANSMISSION.
PARTY‐GOERS INCLUDE
AMBASSADORS FROM THE HUMAN
REFORM LEAGUE NATIONS,
CORPORATE EXECUTIVES,
AND MILITARY PERSONNEL.
ALL OF WHOM CONTRIBUTED
TO THE CONSTRUCTION OF
THE ORBITAL ELEVATOR ITSELF.
MAY I OFFER YOU
A BEVERAGE?
OH!
YES, I'LL TAKE ONE.
(Giggles)
YOU KNOW,
SOME PEOPLE THINK
REAL MEN DON'T BLUSH.
(Giggles)
IT HAS BEGUN,
MY MISTRESS.
FINALLY...
THEY'RE MAKING THEIR MOVE.
HERE COME THE GUNDAM MEISTERS
OF CELESTIAL BEING.
(Gun shots firing)
(Sighs)
Pilot #1:
GOTCHA!
(Firing continues)
Pilot #2:
WHAT MOBILITY!
I NEVER KNEW
A MACHINE COULD DO THAT!
Commander #1:
DON'T BREAK FORMATION!
REINFORCEMENTS ARE
ON THEIR WAY!
AS WE THOUGHT,
THE A. E. U. HAS STATIONED
MILITARY FORCES IN THE PILLAR.
LOCKON.
REINFORCEMENTS APPROACHING.
EVEN SETSUNA WOULD HAVE
TROUBLE IN THIS SITUATION.
WELL, LET'S TAKE AIM
SHALL WE?
LET'S GO!
THE GUNDAM DYNAMES AND
LOCKON STRATOS,
IN OUR MAIDEN BATTLE!
Commander #1:
KEEP YOUR DISTANCE!
IT MAY BE NEW,
BUT THERE'S ONLY ONE!
SURROUND IT!
Pilot #1:
E‐ENEMY ATTACK!
Commander #2
FROM WHERE?!
IT'S FROM BELOW!
IT'S LOCKON.
DYNAMES IS TARGETED
AND READY TO FIRE.
Commander #2:
IT'S FIRING FROM THE GROUND!
(Commander #2 gasps)
AND SO THE SECOND PHASE...
IS NOW COMPLETE.
SO, THAT MOBILE SUIT
IS EXPOSING
THE A. E. U.'S UNDECLARED
FIGHTING STRENGTH?
YEAH!
IT LOOKS TO ME LIKE
IT'S TRYING
TO SHOW THE WORLD THAT
THE A. E. U. HAS MORE
MILITARY POWER
THAN IS ACTUALLY ALLOWED
BY THE TREATY
LIMITATIONS.
THIS IS A CHECK AND
A WARNING.
AND WHY WOULD IT WANT
TO DO THAT?
THAT'S SOMETHING
YOU'RE GOING TO HAVE TO ASK
THE PILOT OF
THAT GUNDAM THING.
BUT YOU KNOW
I REALLY CAN'T SEE
THE A. E. U.
KEEPING
QUIET AFTER THIS.
(Blast)
ANOTHER READING ON
THE E‐SENSOR.
THERE'S BEEN
A LOT OF DEBRIS
FLOATING OUT THERE
TODAY.
IT SURE SEEMS LIKE
AN AWFUL LOT OF MASS.
IT'S PROBABLY JUST
THE REMAINS
OF AN OLD
GENERATION SATELLITE.
Captain:
GET A VISUAL AT
MAXIMUM MAGNIFICATION.
DON'T FORGET THERE'S
A CEREMONY STILL GOING ON.
ROGER THAT, CAPTAIN.
WHAT THE...?
I'M GOING TO TRY TO
ENLARGE THE IMAGE, SIR!
Captain:
THOSE LOOK LIKE MOBILE SUITS!
INCREDIBLE!
THEY SNUCK
IN WITH THE DEBRIS!
IF THEY GET INTERFERENCE
FROM THE SHIELD,
THE MOBILE SUIT,
ALONG WITH THE PILOT,
WILL BE...!
(All gasp)
WHAT'D I TELL YOU?!
IT LOOKS LIKE THESE GUYS
ARE PRETTY DETERMINED.
ARE THEY TERRORISTS?
GIVE THE ORDER FOR THE THIRD
DEFENSE FORCE TO SCRAMBLE!
(Alarm wails)
Pilot #3:
DAMN IT!
ONLY COWARDS
ATTACK DURING A CEREMONY!
Pilot #4:
BUT SIR, I ONLY HAVE
120 HOURS OF SPACE TRAINING!
Commander #3:
WELL THEN JUST CRASH INTO THEM!
YOU'LL GET
A TWO RANK PROMOTION!
Engineer:
THERE WASN'T TIME
TO CHANGE YOUR EQUIPMENT!
YEAH, I KNOW.
THEY'RE USING HELLIONS?
DAMN A. E. U.
THIS IS HAPPENING
BECAUSE THEY'LL SELL WEAPONS
TO ANY LITTLE TIN‐POT NATION.
(People chatter)
OH MY,
EVERYONE WITH A RANK
SEEMS TO ONLY BE
INTERESTED
IN SAVING
THEIR OWN LIVES.
SHALL WE EVACUATE?
OF COURSE NOT.
BUT KUDOS
TO MISS SUMERAGI.
HER FORECAST
WAS REMARKABLY ACCURATE.
Operator #1:
B3 AREA, MAXIMUM PRIORITY.
300 SECONDS UNTIL BACKUP TEAM
SCRAMBLES.
PREVENT UNKNOWNS
FROM ENTERING NON‐COMBAT AREA.
Operator #2:
CONTROL TO ALL UNITS,
UNKNOWNS WILL REACH PILLAR
IN 0‐2‐8‐7.
Commander #3:
ALL UNITS, CONTROL ATTITUDE.
BLOCK THE ENEMY
EN ROUTE!
Pilot #4:
THE ENEMY HAS CHANGED COURSE!
Pilot #3:
DAMN IT!
THEY'RE HIDING BEHIND
THE RING!
Commander #3:
AFTER THEM!
BUT COMMANDER,
WE'RE ON OUR OWN!
STAY FOCUSED, MEN!
(Gun shots firing)
DAMN IT!
THE ENEMY IS GETTING
READY TO OPEN FIRE!
ON COURSE
FOR A DIRECT HIT!
THERE'S NO TIME
TO INTERCEPT THEM!
(Shots firing)
(Rumble)
HUH?
AH! WHAT WAS THAT?!
IT'S A GUNDAM.
GUNDAM KYRIOS.
Commander #3:
WHO THE HELL WAS THAT?!
MISS SUMERAGI'S FORECASTING
REALLY IS AMAZING.
(Firing continues)
Allelujah:
A SUICIDE ATTACK?
THESE TERRORISTS ARE
ALL THE SAME.
TIERIA, COME IN!
THE UNKNOWN IS HEADING
STRAIGHT FOR US!
WHAT?!
(Concerned crowd)
THE VIRTUE.
VIRTUE, PREPARING TO
DESTROY TARGET.
(Boom)
CONFIRMING THIRD PHASE
NOW COMPLETE.
DON'T YOU THINK THAT WAS
JUST A LITTLE BIT EXCESSIVE?
THOSE WERE...
WHAT WERE THEY?
Announcer:
GOOD MORNING.
THIS IS J. N. N. NEWS.
IN OUR LEAD STORY, WE CONTINUE
OUR COVERAGE OF THE ATTACK
ON THE HIGH ORBITAL STATION OF
THE HUMAN REFORM LEAGUE'S
ORBITAL ELEVATOR,
"HEAVEN'S PILLAR".
EARLY THIS MORNING AROUND
DAYBREAK, JAPAN TIME,
THE HUMAN REFORM LEAGUE'S
HIGH ORBITAL STATION
WAS ATTACKED
BY WHAT APPEAR TO HAVE BEEN
TERRORIST MOBILE SUITS.
AT APPROXIMATELY 6:00 P. M.
GREENWICH MEAN TIME,
MOBILE SUITS LAUNCHED
MISSILES
AT THE HIGH ORBITAL STATION,
IN WHAT IS NOW THOUGHT TO BE
A TERRORIST ATTACK.
SUBSEQUENTLY, THE MISSILES
WERE THEN INTERCEPTED
BY AN AS YET
UNIDENTIFIED MOBILE SUIT.
THESE IMAGES WERE TAKEN
BY THE J. N. N. CREW
THAT HAPPENED TO BE
ON LOCATION AT THE TIME.
WHAT'S UP?
WHAT'S GOING ON?
THEY SAY THIS GUY
TOOK OUT ALL
THE TERRORISTS.
IN A MOBILE SUIT?
WHICH MILITARY
IS HE WITH?
APPARENTLY,
THAT'S WHAT THEY
DON'T KNOW.
WHAT DOES ALL OF THIS MEAN?
(Beeping alert)
WE HAVE AN UPDATE
ON THE INCIDENT.
J. N. N. HAS JUST RECEIVED
A VIDEO MESSAGE
FROM AN ORGANIZATION
THAT CLAIMS IT IS RESPONSIBLE
FOR PREVENTING THE ATTACK AND
SAVING THE STATION.
IT'S NOT CLEAR WHO THEY ARE
OR IF THE CLAIMS THEY'RE MAKING
IN THE VIDEO ARE GENUINE.
BUT WHAT IS CLEAR
IS THAT SOMEHOW THEY
ARE INVOLVED IN THE INCIDENT.
NOW, FOR OUR VIEWERS,
WE WILL BROADCAST IT UNEDITED.
I WOULD LIKE
TO ADDRESS THIS STATEMENT
TO EVERY SINGLE HUMAN BEING
BORN AND RAISED ON EARTH.
WE CALL OURSELVES
SIMPLY CELESTIAL BEING.
WE ARE A PRIVATE ARMED
ORGANIZATION
IN POSSESSION
OF THE MOBILE WEAPON GUNDAM.
AN ARMED FORCE?
AND WHAT IS
CELESTIAL BEING?
THE MAIN OBJECTIVE OF
CELESTIAL BEING'S ACTIVITIES
IS TO COMPLETELY ELIMINATE
ACTS OF WAR AND CONFLICT
FROM THIS WORLD.
WE DO NOT ACT FOR
OUR OWN BENEFIT
OR FOR PERSONAL GAIN.
WE HAVE CHOSEN TO INTERVENE FOR
THE GREATEST GOAL OF ALL.
TO RID OURSELVES
OF THE SCOURGE OF WAR.
AS OF THIS MOMENT,
I MAKE THIS DECLARATION
TO ALL HUMANITY...
TERRITORY, RELIGION,
ENERGY,
NO MATTER WHAT
THE REASON OR EXCUSE...
IF THERE IS AN EVIDENT
ACT OF WAR
BEING CARRIED OUT...
WE WILL COMMENCE
INTERVENTION WITH ARMED FORCE.
ANY COUNTRY, ORGANIZATION
OR CORPORATION
THAT PROMOTES WAR
WILL ALSO BE
A LEGITIMATE TARGET
FOR OUR INTERVENTION.
WE SIMPLY CALL OURSELVES
CELESTIAL BEING.
WE ARE AN ARMED ORGANIZATION
THAT WAS
ESTABLISHED TO ELIMINATE
ALL ACTS OF WAR FROM
THIS WORLD.
I REPEAT...
HE'S CLAIMING RESPONSIBILITY?
Patrick:
THOSE ARE THE GUYS?!
THEY'RE THE ONES WHO PUT ME
THROUGH ALL THIS?!
THAT...THAT MAN...
THE WORLD IS
BEGINNING TO CHANGE.
THEY WANT TO SOLVE THE PROBLEM
OF WAR WITH MORE WAR.
(Graham laughing)
NOW THAT'S RICH!
THEY SERIOUSLY WANT TO USE
FORCE TO ELIMINATE WAR?
CELESTIAL BEING...
YOUR WHOLE EXISTENCE
IS A CONTRADICTION!
RIBBONS.
IT HAS BEGUN.
HUMANITY'S REFORMATION.
HALLELUJAH.
IT'S AS IF ALL THE WORLD'S
EVILS ARE EXPOSED.
HUMANITY IS BEING TESTED.
BY THE POWER
OF CELESTIAL BEING.
THAT IS A TERRIBLE MISDEED.
WELL, THIS IS IT.
WE'VE STARTED IT.
AND IT CAN'T BE STOPPED.
IT WON'T STOP!
IT WON'T STOP! IT WON'T STOP!
HEY, WE JUST PICKED
A FIGHT
WITH THE ENTIRE WORLD.
DO YOU KNOW WHAT
THAT MEANS, SETSUNA?
YEAH. I KNOW.
I KNOW BECAUSE
WE'RE THE GUNDAM MEISTERS
OF CELESTIAL BEING.
♪
Narrator:
THE GUNDAMS ARE TO BE
THE MEANS BY WHICH
ALL ACTS OF WAR ARE
REMOVED FROM THE WORLD.
THAT IS WHY THE PILOTS
THEMSELVES
MUST BE DETACHED
FROM THEIR EMOTIONS.
NEXT EPISODE,
"GUNDAM MEISTERS".
IS THIS REALLY
WHAT THE RIGHTEOUS WOULD DO?