Policeman:
BASED ON THE RESULTS
OF THE BIOMETRIC DATA MATCHING,
WE BELIEVE THIS PERSON IS
KINUE CROSSROAD.
PLEASE, WE JUST NEED
A CONFIRMATION.
(Gasps)
KINUE.
(Saji crying)
BUT WHY?
WHY HER?!
KINUE! KINUE!
KINUE!
(Sobbing)
KINUE.
♪
Alejandro:
SO THIS IS
VEDA'S MAINFRAME.
THIS IS AEOLIA SCHENBERG!
OR RATHER,
THE SYSTEM THAT IS
AT THE VERY HEART OF
ALL CELESTIAL BEING'S PLANS!
DO YOU THINK
YOU CAN DO IT, RIBBONS?
YES, BUT I'M GOING TO
REQUIRE SOME TIME TO DO THIS.
I'M NOT CONCERNED.
THE CORNER FAMILY HAS
GREAT PATIENCE.
WE HAVE WAITED OVER
TWO HUNDRED YEARS
FOR THIS MOMENT.
Sumeragi:
CHRIS, ACCESS VEDA.
BRING UP AN IMAGE OF THE TEAM
THAT DROVE OFF THE TRINITYS
ON THE MONITOR.
TRY AND MAKE SURE THE DATA
FROM OUR SIDE DOESN'T‐‐
I'M BLOCKING IT.
READY, FELDT?
I'VE COMPLETED THE DOWNLOAD.
BRINGING UP THE VISUAL.
LOOK AT THAT THING MOVE!
THEY'RE EQUIPPED WITH
PSEUDO SOLAR REACTORS.
(Thinking)
THE FIGHTING IS
ONLY GETTING WORSE.
GUNDAM.
Michael:
HARO!
HAVEN'T YOU BEEN ABLE
TO GET AHOLD OF LAGUNA YET?!
I CAN'T! I CAN'T!
I CAN'T!
NO CONTACT AND THE UN
HAS NEW MACHINES,
WHAT THE HELL'S
GOING ON?!
COME ON, JOHANN,
WHAT DO YOU THINK
WE SHOULD DO NEXT?
Alejandro:
HOW'S IT COMING?
I HAVE ALREADY CLEARED
LEVEL FIVE.
I'M NOW BEGINNING TO
SEIZE CONTROL OF LEVEL SIX.
WELL DONE.
HOW ABOUT A LITTLE INFORMATION
UPDATE TO HELP PASS THE TIME?
HUH.
WELL, LAGUNA HARVEY
SEEMS TO HAVE DISTRIBUTED
ALL OF THE GN‐XS.
AND, IF THAT IS THE CASE,
IT MEANS HE'S ALREADY
PLAYED HIS PART.
(Door opens)
Patrick:
HEY! YOU'RE A FLAG FIGHTER,
AREN'T YOU?
WHO ARE YOU?
(Yelps)
WHAT KIND OF PILOT ARE YOU,
THAT YOU DON'T KNOW ME?!
PATRICK COLASOUR,
NUMBER ONE ACE
OF THE AEU!
YOUR NAME IS
COLASOUR?
UH‐HUH,
THAT'S RIGHT.
OH, RIGHT. YOU'RE THE GUY
WHO GOT HIS ASS KICKED
IN THE GUNDAM'S
FIRST ARMED INTERVENTION.
THAT'S A SORE SPOT
WITH ME!
BY THE WAY, WHERE'S
THE UNION'S TOP GUN HIDING?
CAPTAIN AKER WILL NOT BE
TAKING PART IN THIS OPERATION.
WHAT?
WHAT'S UP WITH THAT?
HUH?
I SEE.
HE GOT SCARED AND
LOST HIS NERVE, DID HE?
THE UNION'S ACE
ISN'T MUCH‐‐
(Chokes)
SOMETHING WRONG?
DON'T INSULT
THE CAPTAIN, GOT IT?!
I DON'T BELIEVE
IN VIOLENCE!
Kati:
THAT'S ENOUGH!
(Relieved sigh)
PLEASE EXCUSE
HIS RUDENESS.
COLONEL!
UNION WARRANT OFFICER
DARYL DODGE, MA'AM.
AND I AM AEU COLONEL
KATI MANNEQUIN.
I'VE BEEN GIVEN COMMAND
OF THIS OPERATION.
NICE TO MEET YOU,
WARRANT OFFICER.
Daryl:
LIKEWISE, MA'AM!
YOU'LL GET MY BEST!
I EXPECT NOTHING LESS.
COME, PATRICK, NOW!
WAIT UP, COLONEL!
WAIT FOR ME!
IF I DON'T TASTE VICTORY,
GIVING UP THE FLAG
WOULD HAVE BEEN POINTLESS.
AND I'LL NEVER BE ABLE
TO FACE THE CAPTAIN.
SORRY, I'VE BEEN
PUSHING YOU SO HARD.
(Gasps)
JUST WHAT I NEEDED!
Christina:
THANKS VERY MUCH!
Sumeragi:
YOU TOO, FELDT!
(Gasps)
BUT THIS IS MY DUTY.
HMM.
HOW'S THE NEW SYSTEM
COMING ALONG?
IT'S ABOUT 80% DONE.
BUT ARE YOU SURE ABOUT THIS?
IF WE HAVE TO CUT THE GUNDAMS
OFF FROM ANY OF VEDA'S SUPPORT,
IT'LL BE TOUGH ON THE PILOTS.
(Chokes)
THERE'S ALCOHOL IN THIS DRINK!
OOPS, SORRY!
(Giggles)
YOU KNOW, YOU'RE NOT AS TENSE
AS YOU USED TO BE, FELDT.
(Gasps)
YOU...YOU REALLY THINK SO?
I DO.
ALL IN ALL, I THINK
IT'S A GOOD TREND.
OKAY. KEEP AT IT JUST
A LITTLE LONGER, PLEASE.
RIGHT!
Thinking:
GIVEN THE EVIDENCE,
IT'S CLEAR THAT SOMEONE IS
MANIPULATING VEDA'S SYSTEMS.
BUT WITHOUT VEDA,
HOW ARE WE EVER GOING TO
BE ABLE TO FIGHT
MACHINES THAT ARE
JUST LIKE OURS?
(Door opens)
Lockon:
SOMETHING ON YOUR MIND?
LOCKON STRATOS.
DON'T WORRY SO MUCH.
IT'S NOT THE END OF THE WORLD IF
WE CAN'T RELY ON VEDA'S SUPPORT.
FOR TWO REASONS.
WE'VE GOT GUNDAMS
AND MISS SUMERAGI'S FORECASTS.
I TAKE IT
YOU DON'T KNOW ABOUT HER PAST.
DO YOU KNOW WHAT KIND OF CRIME
SHE COMMITTED?
I KNOW.
BUT ANYONE CAN MAKE
A MISTAKE.
IN HER CASE, IT JUST HAPPENED
TO BE A VERY BIG ONE.
BUT THE REASON MISS SUMERAGI
CHOSE TO FIGHT
WAS TO ATONE FOR HER PAST.
AND SHE DRINKS TO DROWN
THE REGRET SHE HAS IN HER HEART.
AND THE ONLY REASON
SHE CAN DO THAT
IS BECAUSE
THAT'S WHAT HUMANS DO.
HUMANS...DO IT.
LOCKON,
ARE YOU SAYING
YOU KNOW ABOUT ME?
HMM?
LISTEN GUYS,
MISS SUMERAGI JUST
GAVE ORDERS
FOR US TO STANDBY
IN THE CONTAINERS.
ROGER THAT.
TIERIA, LET ME GET SOMETHING
OFF MY CHEST.
NOW THAT THE TIDE
IS TURNING AGAINST US,
IT'S IMPORTANT
THAT THE FOUR GUNDAMS
COOPERATE WITH EACH OTHER.
LET'S DO THIS.
I GET YOUR POINT,
BUT MAYBE YOU SHOULD BE
SAYING THIS TO SETSUNA F. SEIEI.
YEAH! MAYBE YOU'RE RIGHT
ABOUT THAT.
♪
(Gasps)
Marina:
SORAN.
(Gasps)
PRINCESS
MARINA ISMAIL.
COME LOOK AT SOMETHING,
SORAN.
LOOK HERE.
Marina:
EVEN IN THIS PLACE,
LITTLE FLOWERS
ARE STARTING TO BLOOM.
WITH THE SOLAR POWER,
THE LAND AND THE PEOPLE
WILL REVIVE.
I'M CERTAIN
THINGS WILL GET BETTER.
MARINA.
THE BEST THING IS,
THESE CHANGES MEAN
YOU WON'T HAVE TO FIGHT ANYMORE.
(Gasps)
YOU'VE DONE ENOUGH, SORAN.
(Sighs)
IT WAS ALL JUST A DREAM.
BUT WHY ABOUT MARINA ISMAIL?
BUT, MORE IMPORTANTLY,
DO I WANT TO QUIT?
IS MY MIND REALLY SET ON
QUITTING?
Pilot:
COLONEL, WE'RE ALMOST
AT THE TARGET POINT, SIR.
Sergei:
ROGER THAT.
ATTENTION CHOBU GN‐X TEAM.
WE'RE APPROACHING
THE CELESTIAL BEING FACILITY.
ALL UNITS PREPARE TO ATTACK.
THE SWEET TASTE
OF VICTORY ONCE AGAIN.
COLONEL!
Sergei:
WHAT IS IT?!
HOW'D THEY KNOW
WE WERE COMING FOR THEM?!
Nena:
(Giggles)
THAT'S ONE DOWN!
Michael:
WE ONLY TOOK OUT ONE WITH
THE HIGH‐MEGA?!
YOU'RE THE ONE WHO BETRAYED US.
Johann:
OR PERHAPS,
YOU HAD ALWAYS INTENDED
TO ABANDON US, LAGUNA HARVEY.
MR. HARVEY!
Johann:
THRONES, DISENGAGE DOCKING.
WE'LL CUT RIGHT THROUGH
THE CENTER OF THE ENEMY TEAM!
HUH?
GOOD WORK, GIRLS.
YOU HAVE MY THANKS FOR THIS.
ENEMY ATTACK!
THE FACT THEY WEREN'T
EVEN DETECTED
BY THE E‐SENSOR
UNTIL NOW MEANS...
MISS SUMERAGI.
WHAT IS IT?
BOTH OF YOU GET INTO
YOUR NORMAL SUITS.
Sumeragi:
ALL PERSONNEL, REPORT
TO PRIMARY BATTLE STATIONS.
THE ENEMY TEAM IS 19 MACHINES
EQUIPPED WITH
PSEUDO SOLAR REACTORS!
19.
Sumeragi:
THE ENEMY HAS ALREADY FOUND US!
BUT THAT'S OUR TRICK!
Sumeragi:
EMERGENCY LAUNCH OF THE FOUR
GUNDAMS FROM THEIR CONTAINERS!
INTERCEPT WITH FORMATION S‐34!
THEY'RE VERY CLOSE.
ENEMY TEAM NOW AT 0130.
THEY PROBABLY THOUGHT THEY WERE
GOING TO CATCH US OFF GUARD.
Feldt:
CONTAINERS, OPEN.
Christina:
GUNDAMS, LAUNCHING!
Lockon:
EVERYONE, FORMATION S‐34.
DON'T LET YOUR GUARD DOWN.
ROGER THAT.
ROGER.
♪
Saji:
MY FATHER WAS A
FREELANCE JOURNALIST.
THERE ISN'T A JOURNALIST
WORTH THEIR BYLINE
WHO DOESN'T KNOW
THE NAME OF MR. CROSSROAD.
I'M GUESSING YOUR FATHER
HAD A LOT TO DO
WITH YOUR SISTER
DECIDING TO JOIN OUR COMPANY.
MY FATHER WAS FRAMED BY
A COMPANY HE WAS INVESTIGATING.
HE WENT TO PRISON
FOR THAT.
YEAH, I KNOW.
MY SISTER SAID THAT WHEN
SHE SAW HIM ON VISITING DAYS,
HE WOULD OFTEN SAY THIS TO HER.
"FIRST, SEARCH OUT THE FACTS,
THEN STRING THEM ALL TOGETHER,
AND THAT'S WHEN THE TRUTH
WILL BE REVEALED."
I SEE.
THAT'S WHY KINUE WAS SO‐‐
YOU HAVE TO TELL ME!
HUH?
WHAT WAS THE STORY
MY SISTER WAS INVESTIGATING?!
KINUE'S DEATH WASN'T
JUST AN ACCIDENT,
EVEN I KNOW THAT MUCH!
WHAT WAS SHE
WORKING ON?
(Grunts)
KINUE WAS...
DOING AN IN‐DEPTH INVESTIGATION
OF AEOLIA SCHENBERG.
HUH?
SHE WAS INVESTIGATING WHO?
HE'S THE SCIENTIST
WHO TOLD THE WORLD
HE WAS THE FOUNDER OF
CELESTIAL BEING.
I'M SORRY, SAJI!
IF ONLY I'D STOPPED HER!
(Gasps)
(Sobbing)
KINUE.
Pilot:
I HAVE A VISUAL ON GUNDAMS!
DID THEY REALLY PREDICT
WE WERE GOING TO
LAUNCH AN ATTACK?
IT APPEARS THEY HAVE
A VERY SKILLED COMMANDER.
DOESN'T MATTER TO ME!
I'VE NEVER LOST A MOCK BATTLE.
WHICH MEANS IF
WE'RE IN SIMILAR MACHINES
I HAVE THE ADVANTAGE!
Tieria:
GN FIELD!
(Tieria gasps)
HOW'D THEY BREAK THROUGH
THE FIELD!?
DID THEY SOMEHOW FIGURE OUT
OUR PARTICLE COMPRESSION RATIO?
HUH?
THEY'RE FAST!
TARGETED AND FIRING!
ALL I DID WAS SCRATCH IT!
(Grunts)
THEY FIGHT WELL.
Feldt:
THE TWO LEAD MACHINES ARE
APPROACHING EXIA.
Patrick:
LET'S GO, DARYL!
Daryl:
RIGHT WITH YOU!
(Gasps)
(Growls)
THEY'RE GOOD!
Patrick:
IT'S OUR TURN, BOYS!
GO GET 'EM!
NO ESCAPE POINT!
IS OUR DESTRUCTION PART OF
CELESTIAL BEING'S OVERALL PLAN?!
THAT'S NOT GOING TO HAPPEN!
HOW DARE YOU?!
Tieria:
I'M NOT DONE!
(Beeps)
SOMETHING'S HAPPENED
TO VEDA'S SUPPORT!
Haro:
SYSTEM ERROR! SYSTEM ERROR!
SYSTEM ERROR!
YOU'RE KIDDING ME!
WE'RE EXPENDABLE,
I KNEW IT!
Setsuna:
EXIA!
WHAT'S THE MATTER?!
COME ON, GUNDAM!
(Setsuna yelps)
NOW WE WAIT
AS THEY COME TO PUNISH US
FOR OUR DEEDS.
THIS CAN NOT BE HAPPENING!
THERE'S STILL SO MUCH
FOR US TO DO!
HAS VEDA
MADE THE DECISION
TO ABANDON ME?
Henry:
IT LOOKS LIKE THE GUNDAMS
HAVE STOPPED MOVING!
ARE THEY SETTING A TRAP?
OR IS THIS...
THIS IS JUST LIKE
THAT TIME BEFORE.
HERE I AM IN EXIA
BUT I STILL CAN'T
BECOME A GUNDAM!
I STILL CAN'T!
Ribbons:
MASTER ALEJANDRO,
ARE YOU SURE ABOUT THIS?
Alejandro:
IN ORDER FOR THE WORLD
TO UNITE,
THE UN FORCES MUST BE
VICTORIOUS.
AND AS LONG AS
THE GN DRIVES REMAIN,
CELESTIAL BEING CAN BE
RESURRECTED AT ANY TIME.
I ADMIT I'M A GREEDY MAN
WHO WANTS IT ALL.
THE EARTH AND
CELESTIAL BEING TOO.
I WANT THEM BOTH
FOR MY VERY OWN.
ALL GUNDAM SYSTEMS ARE DOWN!
IT'S AN INTERVENTION BY VEDA!
SWITCH OVER TO OUR OWN SYSTEM
LIKE WE PLANNED!
ROGER!
Setsuna:
IS THIS IT?
IS THIS MY LIFE'S END?
SORAN,
YOU'VE DONE ENOUGH NOW.
(Gasps)
IT'LL BE ALRIGHT.
MARINA.
NO!
I'M STILL ALIVE!
MOVE, EXIA!
COME ON!
GUNDAM, MOVE!
(Machine whirring)
WHAT?
THE SYSTEM'S BACK!
I CAN MOVE!
HUH?
TIERIA!
Christina:
MISS SUMERAGI!
THERE WAS AN ERROR IN
VIRTUE'S SYSTEM TRANSFER!
BUT HOW COME?!
COME ON! MAKE IT IN TIME!
Setsuna:
(Aggressive yell)
THIS GUY!
H‐HE'S MOVING!
TIERIA, WHAT'S THE MATTER?!
(Shuddering)
THE BIG ONE'S NOT MOVING!
HE'S OURS!
(Gasps)
(Nervous grunt)
Patrick:
DAMN YOU!
CRAP!
(Metal clashing)
DO IT NOW!
(Aggressively)
NOT YET!
(Henry screams)
HENRY, NO!
THIS WILL GET ME A KISS
FROM THE COLONEL, ALRIGHT!
(Desponent)
I'M JUST...
HUH?!
(Grunts)
LOCKON!
THIS IS FOR ALL THE HUMILIATION!
Patrick:
(Aggressive yell)
Lockon:
TIERIA!
(Lockon screams in pain)
(Gasps)
Huh?
Tieria:
LOCKON!
Allelujah:
LOCKON! TIERIA,
WHAT'S HAPPENING?!
Patrick:
ONE MORE TIME!
WHAT? WHAT THE?!
SOMEONE NEW?!
NOT A LOT OF PARTICLES LEFT
AFTER THAT BLAST!
BETTER MAKE THEM COUNT!
GOTCHA!
Pilot:
THAT'S THE SIGNAL
TO WITHDRAW!
NO KISS FROM THE COLONEL!
Daryl:
DAMN IT!
I'VE GOT NO EXCUSE FOR
FAILING THE CAPTAIN LIKE THIS!
Lasse:
IS EVERYONE OKAY?
Haro:
DYNAMES DAMAGED!
WHAT?
LOCKON INJURED!
LOCKON'S HURT?!
IT CAN'T BE.
HE WAS PROTECTING ME.
Tieria:
LOCKON STRATOS!
Alejandro:
VERY IMPRESSIVE,
CELESTIAL BEING.
CREATING A BACKUP SYSTEM
IN ADVANCE.
SPLENDID TACTICAL FORECASTING.
THAT'S SUMERAGI LEE NORIEGA
FOR YOU.
ALL GUNDAMS, RETRIEVE
DYNAMES AND VIRTUE!
AND DON'T WASTE TIME!
CHRISTINA,
NOTIFY DR. MORENO.
YES, MA'AM!
LOCKON.
Ribbons:
MASTER ALEJANDRO.
I HAVE JUST FINISHED
CLEARING LEVEL SIX.
HMM.
WE'RE ALMOST THERE.
ALMOST THERE.
NOT A BAD RESULT FOR A TEAM
THAT WAS PUT TOGETHER
IN A HURRY.
Official:
HAVE THEM PROCEED AT FULL SPEED
ON THE MASS PRODUCTION
OF THE GN DRIVES.
YES, THAT'S CORRECT.
THANK YOU.
OUR SIDE HAS NOW
ACQUIRED THE STRENGTH
TO STAND AGAINST THEM AS EQUALS.
Chairman:
PREPARE A PRESS RELEASE.
THE AGE OF THE GUNDAMS
IS OVER.
AND NOW,
THE WORLD WILL CHANGE.
♪
Narrator:
BECAUSE OF ONE MAN,
A PROJECT OVER TWO CENTURIES
IN THE MAKING COLLAPSES.
IS THE CURTAIN ABOUT TO
RISE ON A NEW AGE?
NEXT EPISODE:
"TRANS‐AM".
IS IT WHAT SLEEPS AT
THE BOTTOM OF PANDORA'S BOX?