Sumeragi:
ALLOW ME TO INTRODUCE
OUR NEWEST GUNDAM MEISTER.
HIS CODENAME IS
SETSUNA F. SEIEI.
HE'LL BE PILOTING
THE GN‐001.
AH, HOLD ON A MINUTE,
MISS SUMERAGI.
HE'S STILL JUST A CHILD,
REALLY.
Sumeragi:
HIS PILOTING CHARACTERISTICS
MEET ALL THE STANDARD LEVELS.
WAS IT VEDA
THAT MADE THIS CHOICE?
OF COURSE IT WAS.
Tieria:
I FIND THAT HARD
TO BELIEVE.
Lockon:
WHAT'S THE BIG DEAL?
WE'RE ALL HERE BECAUSE
WE MADE THE DECISION
TO JOIN THIS ORGANIZATION AND
BECOME GUNDAM MEISTERS.
AGE HAS NOTHING
TO DO WITH IT.
ISN'T THAT RIGHT?
AND YOUR NAME IS?
MY CODENAME IS
LOCKON STRATOS.
THE MAN WHO CAN TARGET AND FIRE
FROM BEYOND THE STRATOSPHERE.
I GUESS YOU WANT TO
CHANGE THE WORLD
WITH YOUR GUNDAM TOO, RIGHT?
YES.
WELL, SO DO I,
SETSUNA.
Haro:
LOCKON! LOCKON!
(Incessant)
SO DO I,
LOCKON STRATOS.
Haro (repeating):
LOCKON! LOCKON!
(Weeping)
LOCKON STRATOS...
(Gasps)
(Screaming)
♪
MISTRESS, YOU SHOULD KNOW
WE JUST RECEIVED
A SPECIAL ENCODED
MESSAGE FROM THE PTOLEMAIOS.
CONCERNING WHAT?
"WE'VE BEGUN
EXCHANGING FIRE
WITH THE UN FORCES MOBILE SUITS
EQUIPPED WITH PSEUDO GN DRIVES."
THAT'S ALL.
I SEE.
Liu Mei:
I WONDER WHICH SIDE
THE WORLD WILL LEAN TOWARDS.
THE UN'S OR THEIRS?
Tieria:
IT WAS YOU!
TAKE IT EASY,
TIERIA!
BECAUSE YOU WENT DOWN TO THE SURFACE
BECAUSE YOU WENT DOWN
TO THE SURFACE
OUR FIGHTING STRENGTH
WAS CRITICALLY DIVIDED!
Tieria:
ANSWER ME!
WHY DID HE HAVE TO DIE?
WHY DID HE... HAVE TO DIE?
HUH?
THE ENEMY'S STILL OUT THERE!
USE THIS TIME TO HELP US
INSTEAD OF COMPLAINING!
(Weeping)
SORRY, FELDT.
IT ISN'T YOUR FAULT, HARO.
YOU DON'T HAVE TO
APOLOGIZE.
(Crying)
OH, FELDT.
IT'S MOMENTS LIKE THIS
THAT ARE THE WORST.
Sergei:
OUT OF THE 27 MACHINES
ONLY 11 WERE ABLE TO
MAKE IT BACK.
WE EVEN LOST THE MACHINE
WE'D CAPTURED EARLIER.
ALSO, THE GUNDAMS
SEEM TO HAVE NEW ABILITIES.
COLONEL MANNEQUIN,
I SUGGEST WE WITHDRAW FROM
THIS AIRSPACE, AT LEAST FOR NOW.
CONTINUING WOULD NEEDLESSLY RISK
THE LIVES OF OUR SOLDIERS.
I DO AGREE WITH YOU,
BUT UN HEADQUARTERS SAYS
IT'S SENDING REINFORCEMENTS
TO BOLSTER OUR NUMBERS.
THEY HAVE REINFORCEMENTS?
DO YOU MEAN THE UN
HAS MORE MACHINES
EQUIPPED WITH THOSE
GN DRIVES?
I DON'T KNOW.
BUT OUR ORDERS ARE TO LAUNCH
A SECOND ASSAULT
AS SOON AS THEY GET HERE.
(Beeping)
I'M DETECTING A GN‐X
APPROACHING THE SHIP, COLONEL.
REALLY?
MUST BE ANOTHER SURVIVOR.
Operator 23B:
WE HAVE A MATCH ON
THE MACHINE.
THE PILOT IS LIEUTENANT
PATRICK COLASOUR OF THE AEU.
SORRY, I LET YOU DOWN,
COLONEL.
THEY KIND OF DID
A NUMBER ON ME.
YOU REALLY HAD ME
WORRIED THERE
YOU SILLY DUMBASS.
(Thinking)
THAT WINGED GUNDAM.
IT WASN'T AFFECTED BY
MY QUANTUM BRAIN WAVES.
CAN IT BLOCK THEM OUT NOW?
OR MAYBE...
WHATEVER THE CASE, I'LL
SETTLE THIS IN THE NEXT BATTLE!
I AM A PERFECT SUPER‐SOLDIER.
I'M NOT ABOUT TO LOSE TO
THAT INFERIOR SUBJECT E‐57!
Ian:
WELL, AS YOU INSTRUCTED,
I DEPLOYED SOME SATELLITES
THAT ARE EMITTING GN PARTICLES.
BUT DO YOU THINK THE ENEMY WILL
REALLY FALL FOR THIS TRICK?
IT CAN'T HURT TO TRY.
AND YOU KNOW
THEY'RE GOING TO BE
WATCHING THE ASTEROID FIELD
CLOSELY.
WE NEED TO TRY EVERYTHING
WE POSSIBLY CAN.
AND, WHAT'S THE STATUS
ON THE GUNDAMS?
KYRIOS IS GOOD TO GO
ONCE WE REMOVE ITS FLIGHT UNIT.
WITH VIRTUE, WE'LL STRIP
ITS OUTER ARMOR
AND DEPLOY IT AS NADLEEH.
I'VE PREPARED
WEAPONS FOR IT, TOO.
HOW LONG UNTIL YOU'RE ALL DONE?
IT'S GOING TO TAKE US
AT LEAST EIGHT HOURS.
HAVE IT FINISHED IN SIX HOURS,
PLEASE.
GOTCHA.
(Sighs)
(Thinking)
RIGHT NOW, THE ONLY THINGS
WE CAN COUNT ON IN A FIGHT
ARE THE ASSAULT CONTAINERS,
EXIA AND THE GN ARMS.
THE TRANS‐AM IS OUR SAFETY NET,
BUT IT HAS A TIME LIMIT.
HUH?
TIERIA?
SUMERAGI LEE NORIEGA,
WHEN IT'S DONE,
PLEASE SUBMIT
YOUR NEXT MISSION PLAN.
(Gasp)
YOU WANT TO GO BACK AND
FIGHT ALREADY?
OF COURSE I DO.
WIPING OUT THE REMAINING
ENEMY MACHINES
EQUIPPED WITH THE
PSEUDO GN DRIVES
WOULD PROVE TO THE WORLD
HOW STRONG WE STILL ARE.
THEN WE COULD CONTINUE
WITH THE PLAN.
BUT THE RISK HERE IS ENORMOUS.
AND THE ENEMY COULD HAVE
REINFORCEMENTS.
I UNDERSTAND.
BUT YOU SHOULD KNOW
I'M NOT THE ONLY ONE
WHO'S THINKING
LIKE THIS.
ALL THE
MEISTERS FEEL THIS WAY.
HUH?
ALLELUJAH, TOO?
AND SETSUNA?
PLEASE.
(Thinking)
WE SIMPLY HAVE TO SURVIVE.
ALI AL‐SAACHEZ!
HE WAS THE ONE
WHO KILLED LOCKON!
BOTH OF MY PARENTS AND MY LITTLE
SISTER WERE KILLED BY THE KPSA
IN AN ATTACK
BY A SUICIDE BOMBER.
LET ME AVENGE MY FAMILY'S DEATH.
LET ME SETTLE THIS SCORE.
IN A DESPERATE BID
FOR REVENGE,
DID YOU
THROW AWAY YOUR LIFE, LOCKON?
WHAT'S THE MATTER WITH YOU?
WHAT'S WRONG...
ARE YOU AFRAID OF DYING?
THAT'S BLASPHEMY AGAINST GOD!
AFTER DEATH,
THERE IS NO GOD.
Lasse (flashback):
AT THIS POINT, I THINK
CELESTIAL BEING'S EXISTENCE,
THAT WE EXIST,
MIGHT HAVE A CERTAIN LASTING
SIGNIFICANCE ALL BY ITSELF.
(Gasps)
WHAT IT MEANS TO EXIST,
THAT IS,
WHAT IT MEANS TO BE ALIVE,
IS TO FACE THE WORLD
AND TRY TO CARRY ON THE IDEAS
OF THOSE WHO'VE DIED.
AND NOT FOR GOD...
I'LL DO IT BY MY OWN WILL.
Operator 23A:
MESSAGE FROM
OBSERVATION TEAM 34.
THEY'VE DETECTED
FOUR OBJECTS
MOVING AWAY FROM
THE ASTEROID FIELD.
HAVE THE RECON TEAM
PATROLLING THE ASTEROIDS'
PERIMETER CONFIRM THIS.
YES, MA'AM!
IT'S A DIVERSION.
YES, I'M SURE IT IS.
Operator 23B:
MA'AM, SILHOUETTE APPROACHING
FROM BEHIND US!
HUH?
WHAT KIND OF MACHINE IS THAT?
I WONDER.
IS THAT SOMETHING ELSE THAT
WAS TAKEN FROM CELESTIAL BEING?
Lichtendahl:
REALLY?
SO, SETSUNA AND THE OTHER
MEISTERS HAVE DECIDED TO FIGHT?
THAT MEANS BE PREPARED
FOR THE WORST.
MAN, THAT'S A SCARY THOUGHT!
Feldt:
REALLY WE'VE GOT NO CHOICE
BUT TO FIGHT.
HUH?
WHAT ARE YOU DOING, FELDT?
IT'S A LETTER.
A LETTER?
(Sighs)
IT'S TO MY MOM AND DAD
IN HEAVEN.
AND THERE'S ONE TO LOCKON.
FELDT, YOUR PARENTS ARE...
WRITING A WILL'S SUPPOSED
TO BE BAD LUCK!
IT'S NOT A WILL!
I PLAN ON STAYING ALIVE.
AND I WON'T SEE THEM
FOR A WHILE.
SO I'M APOLOGIZING.
(Realizing)
I SEE.
THAT'S THE SPIRIT, FELDT.
I PROMISED LOCKON THAT
I'D SURVIVE.
GOOD, MAKE SURE
YOU KEEP THAT PROMISE.
HEY, YOU KNOW, MAYBE I SHOULD
BE WRITING A LETTER AS WELL.
YEAH, TO WHO?
MY MOM IN THE COLONIES.
HMM?
THE WOMAN WHO RAISED ME.
THOUGH I DON'T REALLY HAVE
FOND MEMORIES.
I KIND OF RAN AWAY FROM THERE.
THEN VEDA CHOSE ME.
AT LEAST
YOU HAVE SOMEONE.
YOU CAN
SAY THAT AGAIN.
SO WHAT ABOUT YOU,
LICHTY?
MY MOM AND DAD
WERE BOTH ENGINEERS
WHO WORKED ON ONE OF
THE ORBITAL ELEVATORS.
WHEN I WAS JUST A KID
THEY CASHED IN THEIR CHIPS
IN THE SOLAR POWER WARS.
EVERYONE'S GOT A STORY.
WELL IT'S BECAUSE
OF OUR STORIES
THAT WE ALL JOINED UP
WITH CELESTIAL BEING.
COME TO THINK OF IT,
THIS IS THE FIRST TIME
WE'VE EVER TALKED ABOUT
EACH OTHER'S PASTS LIKE THIS.
WE WERE SWORN TO
CONFIDENTIALITY.
BUT THAT
DOESN'T MATTER NOW.
YOU'RE RIGHT
ABOUT THAT.
(Sighs)
SO, HOW'S NADLEEH DOING?
THEY'RE ALL DONE.
BUT THERE'S NO MORE
TRIAL SYSTEM, IS THERE?
AND NADLEEH DOESN'T HAVE A LOT
OF PARTICLE STORAGE CAPACITY‐‐
I'M STILL DOING IT.
THERE'S NO CHOICE.
I HAVE TO TAKE REVENGE
FOR LOCKON.
MAYBE YOU SHOULDN'T GET
SO WORKED UP ABOUT THIS.
I NEED TO FINISH THIS.
Feldt:
SETSUNA.
FELDT GRACE,
WHAT'S THE MATTER?
I WROTE
A LETTER TO LOCKON.
IS THERE ANYONE YOU WANT TO
WRITE A LETTER TO, SETSUNA?
NO, THERE ISN'T.
I SEE.
HOW LONELY FOR YOU.
NO, HE'S THE LONELY ONE.
SO HARO,
YOU STAY BY HIS SIDE.
HERE, NEXT TO LOCKON.
LOCKON! LOCKON!
KEEP HIM COMPANY, HARO.
ROGER! ROGER!
THANKS SO MUCH.
(Siren rings)
(Gasps)
Christina:
THE E‐SENSOR HAS PICKED UP
SOMETHING. ENEMY TEAM DETECTED.
COME ON, FELDT. LET'S GO.
RIGHT.
HOW MANY MACHINES
IN THE ENEMY TEAM?
13 OF THEM! BUT THERE'S
A REALLY BIG ONE
IN THE MIDDLE OF
THE ENTIRE GROUP!
WHAT KIND OF
BIG ONE?
I'LL PUT IT
ON THE MONITOR!
SORRY I'M LATE.
(Gasps)
IS THAT SOME KIND
OF BATTLESHIP?
NO LICHTY.
I'M AFRAID NOT.
THAT'S A MOBILE ARMOR
LOADED WITH PSEUDO GN DRIVES!
(Confidently)
HMM.
(Blast)
IT'S FIRING A PARTICLE BEAM!
FROM THAT FAR AWAY?
OH MAN!
(Crash)
Feldt:
NUMBER ONE PARTICLE EMITTER
WAS HIT.
Sumeragi:
TRANSFER PARTICLE SUPPLY TO
NUMBER TWO EMITTER!
Feldt:
ROGER!
SECOND SHOT COMING IN!
LICHTY, MOVE!
YEAH, I'M ON IT!
(Blast)
(Screaming)
LAUNCH THE ASSAULT CONTAINER!
YOUR TARGET'S
THE ENEMY MOBILE ARMOR!
ROGER.
ASSAULT CONTAINER IS PREPPED
AND HEADING OUT!
(Powering up)
KEEP THE PTOLEMY HIDDEN BEHIND
THE ASTEROIDS, LICHTY.
ROGER THAT!
Sumeragi:
KYRIOS AND NADLEEH LAUNCH
STRAIGHT FROM THE CONTAINERS.
PROTECT PTOLEMY!
Allelujah:
ROGER THAT!
ROGER!
Sergei:
STICK TO THE PLAN
AND ENGAGE THEIR SPACESHIP
IN A TWO‐PRONGED ATTACK.
USE THE ASTEROIDS
TO COVER YOUR APPROACH,
AND THEN DESTROY IT!
All together:
ROGER!
NOW IT'S MY TURN TO
WIN SOME GLORY!
HIGH VELOCITY OBJECT
APPROACHING FROM DEAD AHEAD!
Peries:
AN ENEMY!
COLONEL!
Sergei:
LEAVE IT TO ALVATORE!
Peries:
YES, SIR!
Sergei: LEAVE IT TO ALVATORE!
THIS TIME WE'LL BRING THE BATTLE
TO A CLEAR DECISIVE END!
Christina:
ENEMY MOBILE SUITS APPROACHING
FROM PORT AND STARBOARD!
Pilot 24A:
G... GUNDAM!
YOU WILL NOT GET PAST ME!
Patrick:
WHERE THE HELL'S YOUR ARMOR?
(Grunting)
IT'S TOO EARLY TO USE
THE TRANS‐AM!
Peries (gasping):
WHAT'S WRONG?
HUH?
(Hallelujah cackling)
Peries:
THAT SUIT...IT'S YOU!
I'M SORRY, ALLELUJAH...
BUT YOU KNOW WHAT?
I DON'T WANT
TO DIE JUST YET!
SUBJECT E‐57!
Hallelujah:
THAT'S ME.
(Gasps)
Sergei:
LEAVE THIS ONE TO ME!
(Laughing wickedly)
WE'RE IN RANGE!
TIME TO LAUNCH THE ATTACK!
(Barrage of shots)
A GN FIELD? HOW DID THESE GUYS
MAKE ONE SO STRONG?
(Growling)
Lasse:
IN THAT CASE, HOW ABOUT THIS!
(Blast)
PTOLEMY, WATCH OUT!
(Pilot 24B screaming)
(Blast)
WHAT'S THIS?
(Hallelujah screaming)
(All screaming)
(Gasping)
IT HIT THE PTOLEMAIOS!
(Determined grunt)
DAMN, YOU FILTHY BASTARDS!
Feldt:
CONTAINERS THREE AND FOUR
SERIOUSLY DAMAGED!
STARBOARD SIDE IS WRECKED!
LOWER SHUTTERS
E‐20 TO 68!
ROGER THAT!
MISS SUMERAGI,
SICKBAY WAS HIT!
YOU SHOULDN'T HAVE GONE OFF
BY YOURSELF, YOU SCREW‐UP!
BUT THAT MEANS...
Feldt:
THERE'S A PROBLEM
WITH THE SYSTEM!
WE CAN'T GENERATE A GN FIELD!
DAMN IT.
I'LL HEAD TO
THE ASSAULT CONTAINER!
WE'VE GOT TO HIT BACK!
LET IAN KNOW!
ROGER!
ENOUGH OF THIS!
Tieria:
TRANS‐AM!
WHAT THE HELL IS THIS?
NADLEEH READY TO DESTROY!
...THE HELL?
(Screaming)
LUCKY BREAK FOR ME!
IT CAN'T BE OVER.
I CAN'T
DIE YET!
(Rapid blasting)
FOR THE SAKE OF OUR PLAN.
AND ALSO...
DIE, GUNDAM!
FOR THE SAKE OF LOCKON!
HUH?
YOU BASTARDS REALLY
SUCK AT THIS, DON'T YOU?
(Grunting)
Sergei:
THEY'RE STILL ALIVE!
(Determined growl)
COME ON, HIT THEM!
Christina:
FELDT!
YES?
THERE'S SOMETHING WRONG WITH
DYNAMES' SOLAR REACTOR.
THERE MAY BE A PROBLEM
WITH THE LINKAGE.
I DON'T HAVE
ANY DATA ON THAT.
HURRY UP OR AT THIS RATE
WE'RE FINISHED!
ROGER!
THAT'S A LIE, ISN'T IT?
YOU COULD TELL?
YEAH, TOTALLY.
LICHTY, THERE'S
A MACHINE HEADING FOR US!
WE'RE GOING TO MAKE IT
THROUGH THIS!
I KNOW WE ARE,
I JUST HOPE FELDT ISN'T TOO MAD
AT ME AFTER ALL THIS!
FIRE GN MISSILES!
HE'S TRYING TO GET IN
OUR BLIND SPOT!
I WON'T LET HIM!
I'M SEPARATING THE CONTAINER
FROM THE PTOLEMY.
WHAT'S HAPPENING?
IT'S FELDT!
HERE HE COMES!
(Gasping)
CHRIS!
(Blast)
(Boom)
CHRISTINA! LICHTY!
WHY YOU!
(Boom)
COME IN, CHRIS!
LICHTY, RESPOND!
Sumeragi:
PLEASE! CHRIS!
LICHTY...
(Gasps)
Lichty:
I'M OKAY.
(Wincing)
I WAS CAUGHT UP IN IT.
WITH MY PARENTS AND HALF OF
MY BODY ENDED UP LIKE THIS.
I DON'T KNOW IF I'M HALF DEAD
OR HALF ALIVE.
LICHTY.
I'M SUCH A SILLY FOOL.
THERE WAS THIS AMAZING GUY
RIGHT NEXT TO ME
THIS ENTIRE TIME.
YEAH, YOU'RE RIGHT.
I JUST COULDN'T SEE IT.
I WAS BLIND.
YEAH.
YOU WERE.
OH, LICHTY.
♪
(Radio static)
Sumeragi:
... COME IN! CHRIS!
(Radio buzzing)
Christina:
MISS SUMERAGI.
CHRIS, THANK HEAVENS YOU'RE
ALIVE! IS LICHTY ALL RIGHT?
(Sighs)
Christina:
FELDT, ARE YOU THERE?
I'M HERE.
I'D LIKE YOU TO...
TRY HARDER...
TO STAY IN FASHION.
WHY ARE YOU SAYING THIS?
Christina:
AND YOU HAVE TO LIVE
FOR LOCKON, TOO.
(Tearful sigh)
(Coughing)
PLEASE DO IT.
CHANGE THIS WORLD. CHANGE IT...
PLEASE.
(Electrical buzzing)
(Boom)
CHRIS!
LICHTY!
(Tearful gasp)
(Sobbing)
Feldt (screaming):
CHRISTINA SIERRA!
OUR ATTACKS ARE INEFFECTIVE!
IN THAT CASE, WE'LL DIVE
RIGHT INTO HIM!
Lasse:
AND BLAST HIM UP CLOSE!
YES!
HMM?
WHAT?
(Alejandro laughing)
Alejandro:
YOU IRRITATING GHOSTS
OF AEOLIA SCHENBERG!
YOU SHOULD BE HONORED THAT I,
ALEJANDRO CORNER,
WILL OFFER YOU UP
AS SACRIFICES
FOR MY NEW WORLD!
JUST TRY IT!
DAMN.
SETSUNA!
EXIA.
SETSUNA F. SEIEI...
... WILL ELIMINATE THE TARGET!
♪
Narrator:
KYRIOS IS FALLEN.
NADLEEH IS FALLEN.
EXIA IS FALLEN.
LIFE MINGLES WITH DEATH.
NEXT EPISODE:
"SETSUNA".
IN A TIME OF REFORMATION,
REBIRTH HAS COME FROM
DESTRUCTION.
A YOUNG MAN GROANS IN PAIN.