(Alejandro laughing)
Alejandro:
YOU IRRITATING GHOSTS OF
AEOLIA SCHENBERG!
YOU SHOULD BE HONORED THAT I,
ALEJANDRO CORNER,
WILL OFFER YOU UP
AS SACRIFICES
FOR MY NEW WORLD!
JUST TRY IT!
DAMN.
SETSUNA!
EXIA.
SETSUNA F. SEIEI...
... WILL ELIMINATE THE TARGET!
(Sighing)
Lasse:
SETSUNA!
TARGET THE CONTAINER!
IF IT WORKS, YOU COULD AT LEAST
BLOW ITS ARMS OFF!
ROGER THAT!
WELL, DID IT WORK?
NEGATIVE.
Lasse (frustrated):
IT'S NOT EVEN SCRATCHED!
(Chuckling wickedly)
YOU'RE TRYING TO FIGHT
THE ALVATORE
WITH JUST THAT
PATHETIC LITTLE THING?
WHY THAT'S SIMPLY LAUGHABLE!
♪
Sumeragi:
FELDT, GIVE ME THE STATUS
OF THE MEISTERS.
Feldt:
NADLEEH IS BADLY DAMAGED.
THERE'S NO RESPONSE
FROM TIERIA.
THERE'S NO RESPONSE?
KYRIOS HAS SERIOUS
BODY DAMAGE.
IT'S BEING ENGAGED BY
TWO ENEMY MOBILE SUITS.
Sumeragi:
COME ON, GUYS.
Sergei:
THE WINGED ONE IS HIDING AMONG
THESE ASTEROIDS.
IN ITS CONDITION,
IT CAN'T HAVE GONE VERY FAR.
DAMN IT,
I REALLY SCREWED UP.
HALLELUJAH.
HUH? STAY OUT
OF THIS, ALLELUJAH.
HALLELUJAH
HUH? STAY OUT
OF THIS, ALLELUJAH.
YOU'RE USELESS
WHEN IT COMES TO
THESE KINDS OF LIFE
AND DEATH SITUATIONS.
I AM GOING TO LIVE,
EVEN IF I HAVE TO
DRINK THE BLOOD OF OTHERS!
LOOK, I WANT TO
LIVE TOO!
YOU DO?
I HAVEN'T HEARD
THE WORLD'S ANSWER
TO EVERYTHING
THAT'S HAPPENED.
THE MEANING OF OUR STRUGGLE.
AND UNTIL I LEARN WHAT IT IS,
I WON'T DIE!
(Chuckles)
FINALLY, YOU'RE GETTING
THE RIGHT ATTITUDE!
SO HOW ABOUT YOU AND I
SHOW THAT WOMAN THERE
WHAT IT'S LIKE TO FACE
A REAL SUPER‐SOLDIER!
Sergei:
HERE IT COMES!
SET A DIRECT COURSE.
THEY'RE NOT GETTING AWAY!
(Gasps)
Allelujah:
LINE UP THE AXIS...
Hallelujah: USE THE LEG!
Hallelujah:
USE THE LEG!
Allelujah:
WE ATTACK TOGETHER!
(Moaning)
LIEUTENANT!
(Attacking yell)
C‐COLONEL!
Sergei:
HE'S MOVING DIFFERENTLY!
Peries:
BUT HOW,
WITH HIS MACHINE LIKE THAT?
Hallelujah:
THINGS ARE GOING TO BE
DIFFERENT FROM NOW ON!
YOU SAID IT, HALLELUJAH!
THESE WEAPONS ARE
THE SAME AS THAT THRONE'S!
Lasse:
SETSUNA! LET'S DOCK.
ROGER THAT!
(Boom)
THE GN ARMOR IS NOTHING.
FANGS, FLY!
Lasse:
GENERATING FIELD!
I'M TAKING THEM OUT!
(Blast)
(Boom)
A SKILLFUL EVASION.
TRY THIS!
Lasse:
GET CLOSER, SETSUNA!
IS THAT ALL YOU KNOW
HOW TO DO?
WHAT THE...?
YOU'RE DEAD MEAT!
(Blast)
Lasse:
I'M NOT DONE YET!
JUST ONE MORE PASS!
SETSUNA, REMEMBER WHAT I SAID
ABOUT WHY WE EXIST‐‐
(Gasping)
LASSE!
(Growling)
YOU DAMNED BASTARD!
(Setsuna yelling fiercely)
(Groaning)
(Electrical buzzing)
(Setsuna yelling)
(Gasping)
BUT HOW?
(Attacking yell)
(Setsuna yelling)
(Setsuna screams aggressively)
(Boom)
THIS...THIS CAN'T BE!
A SINGLE GUNDAM IS
DESTROYING MY ALVATORE!
(Rapid blasting)
(Sergei yells)
COLONEL!
(Blasting rapidly)
HUH?
(Gasps)
Peries:
WHAT'S HAPPENING?
I'M SUPPOSED TO BE
THE PERFECT SUPER SOLDIER!
Hallelujah:
YOU JUST DON'T
GET IT, WOMAN .
GET WHAT?
YOU'RE FAR FROM BEING
A PERFECT SUPER‐SOLDIER!
YOUR QUANTUM BRAIN WAVES
GIVE YOU SUPER REFLEXES,
BUT OBVIOUSLY YOUR MIND
IS TOO SLUGGISH
TO KEEP UP WITH
THAT KIND OF REACTION SPEED!
YOU'RE JUST ACTING ON INSTINCT,
LIKE AN ANIMAL!
NO, THAT'S NOT TRUE!
Hallelujah:
THAT'S WHY I CAN PREDICT
YOUR ACTIONS.
(Peries gasps)
Hallelujah:
REFLEXES AND THOUGHT
MUST BE ONE.
THIS SYNTHESIS IS THE MARK OF
A TRUE SUPER‐SOLDIER!
IT'S BEGINNING TO GLOW!
THAT EFFECT AGAIN!
Peries:
DAMN YOU!
Sergei:
DAMN YOU! LIEUTENANT
LIEUTENANT!
(Peries yelling)
(Groaning)
(Gasping)
Hallelujah:
THIS IS FAREWELL, WOMAN!
Sergei:
LIEUTENANT!
(Yelling)
COLONEL!
NOW!
NOW, PERIES!
(Screaming aggressively)
(Screaming)
Peries:
COLONEL! COLONEL!
(Hatch opening)
HUH?
(Struggling)
Sergei:
WHAT ARE YOU DOING?
NEVER MIND ABOUT ME!
KEEP FIGHTING, LIEUTENANT!
I CAN'T!
HUH?
IF YOU WERE GONE, COLONEL,
I'D BE ALL ALONE.
(Sympathetic)
LIEUTENANT.
(Pained breathing)
(Beeping)
(Confused)
HMM?
HUH?
Allelujah:
M‐MARIE! BUT HOW?
WHY ARE YOU...
LASSE! RESPOND IF YOU CAN,
LASSE!
(Noticing)
HUH?
WHAT?
ANOTHER ONE!
(Alejandro yelling)
Alejandro:
THE MACHINES WITH
THE ORIGINAL SOLAR REACTORS
ARE QUITE IMPRESSIVE.
TO HAVE CAUSED ME
THIS MUCH TROUBLE,
EVEN WITH A NOVICE PILOT!
SO YOU'RE THE ONE WHO TWISTED
AEOLIA'S ORIGINAL PLAN!
THIS IS ALL
ACCORDING TO THE PLAN!
THE ONLY DIFFERENCE NOW IS
I'VE BECOME THE LEAD ACTOR!
OH, YES!
THE LEAD ROLE BELONGS TO ME,
ALEJANDRO CORNER!
Setsuna:
WHAT DO YOU WANT
OUT OF ALL THIS?
Alejandro:
DESTRUCTION AND REBIRTH.
WHAT?
CELESTIAL BEING'S
ARMED INTERVENTIONS
HAVE DESTROYED
THE WORLD AS WE KNEW IT.
SO THAT IT CAN BE
REBORN IN UNITY!
AND NOW I WILL MAKE SURE
THAT THE WORLD IS REMADE
IN MY IMAGE!
Setsuna:
YOU'RE SAYING
YOU WANT TO RULE THE WORLD?
I'M SAYING I'LL GUIDE IT
PROPERLY!
BUT, IN THAT NEW WORLD,
THERE IS NO PLACE FOR YOU!
YOU'LL BE SWEPT AWAY LIKE DUST!
DIE, EXIA!
(Blast)
(Alejandro laughing)
(Laughing wickedly)
HOW UNFORTUNATE FOR YOU,
AEOLIA SCHENBERG!
THE ONE WHO WILL
ACTUALLY UNITE THE WORLD
AND GUIDE HUMANITY INTO
A NEW ERA WILL BE ME,
A PERSON WHO IS
LIVING IN THE PRESENT!
(Alarm beeping)
HUH?
IS...IS THAT‐‐
Alejandro:
EXIA!
DAMN AEOLIA'S SYSTEM!
Setsuna:
I'VE FOUND IT.
FOUND WHAT?
I'VE FOUND THE TWISTED
DISTORTION IN THIS WORLD!
THAT'S RIGHT!
(Screaming)
AND YOU'RE THE ONE RESPONSIBLE!
Alejandro:
THE REBIRTH
HAS ALREADY BEGUN!
YET YOU CONTINUE
TO DESTROY!
OF COURSE I DO!
HIS GN FIELD!
(Growling)
Lockon:
SETSUNA,
DO YOU KNOW WHY
EXIA IS EQUIPPED WITH
A PHYSICAL SWORD?
IT'S A COUNTERMEASURE
AGAINST GN FIELDS.
THE PLAN HAS PROVISIONS
FOR FIGHTING AGAINST
OTHER GUNDAMS AS WELL.
IF THAT WERE TO HAPPEN,
YOU WOULD BE OUR TRUMP CARD.
WE'RE COUNTING ON YOU,
SETSUNA.
(Thinking)
I KNOW, LOCKON. I'M A DESTROYER
WHO KNOWS ONLY HOW TO FIGHT.
BUT I FIGHT TO DEFEAT THOSE
WHO BRING ABOUT CONFLICT!
AND NOW I'LL DESTROY
THE TWISTEDNESS!
YOU BASTARD!
Setsuna:
THE ERADICATION OF WAR
THROUGH FORCE!
THAT IS CELESTIAL BEING!
MY FIELD IS GONE!
Setsuna:
AND THE GUNDAM WILL DO IT!
TOGETHER WITH ME!
THAT'S RIGHT!
THAT'S WHAT I AM!
WHAT ALL OF US ARE!
WE'RE GUNDAMS!
(Electricity flashing)
HMM?
RI... RIBBONS...
ALEJANDRO CORNER.
YOU PLAYED THE JESTER SO WELL.
I WHAT?
I SHOULD TELL YOU
THIS IS NO LONGER
AEOLIA SCHENBERG'S PLAN.
YOU SEE,
IT HAS NOW BECOME MY PLAN.
(Struggling)
BUT, RIBBONS! HOW COULD YOU!
KNOW THAT YOU'LL BE LEAVING
THE FUTURE
OF THE UNIFIED WORLD
IN MY HANDS.
YOU TRAITOR! THIS IS
THE CORNER FAMILY'S DREAM!
THAT OBSESSION IS PRECISELY
WHAT MAKES YOU SUCH
A SMALL MAN.
RIBBONS!
(Boom)
(Panting)
(Beeping)
Setsuna:
THERE'S ANOTHER ONE?
(Gasping)
IT'S A FLAG!
WITH A PSEUDO SOLAR REACTOR!
Graham:
I'VE SO WANTED TO MEET YOU.
I'VE WANTED TO MEET YOU
SO MUCH. GUNDAM!
THAT'S A BEAM SABER!
(Gasping)
Graham:
I WILL AVENGE HOWARD AND DARYL
WITH THIS GN FLAG!
HE'S HAILING ME!
(Gasps)
SO IT'S YOU!
Graham:
WHAT'S THIS?
YOU'RE THAT BOY!
IT SEEMS THAT OUR DESTINIES
HAVE BEEN CONNECTED ALL ALONG!
Graham:
INDEED! WE WERE DESTINED
TO FIGHT EACH OTHER!
Graham:
I FINALLY UNDERSTAND!
(Setsuna growls)
Graham: IT WAS YOUR
DISPLAY OF OVERWHELMING POWER
THAT STOLE MY HEART!
THAT FEELING I HAD,
CAN ONLY BE CALLED LOVE!
LOVE?
BUT IF YOU GO BEYOND LOVE,
IT BECOMES HATRED.
JUST AS PEOPLE TURN ON
EACH OTHER
WHEN THEY TAKE
RELIGIOUS FAITH TOO FAR!
(Growling)
IF YOU KNOW SO MUCH ABOUT IT,
THEN WHY
DO YOU STILL FIGHT?
Graham:
YOU'RE ASKING A SOLDIER
WHY HE FIGHTS?
DON'T BE RIDICULOUS!
Setsuna:
YOU'VE BECOME TWISTED!
Graham:
YOU MADE ME THIS WAY!
(Growling)
Graham:
THIS IS BECAUSE
THE GUNDAMS EXIST!
THAT'S THE REAL REASON
I'M TAKING YOU OUT!
I DON'T CARE ABOUT
THE REST OF THE WORLD.
THIS IS MY OWN WILL!
DON'T KID YOURSELF!
YOU'RE A PART OF THIS WORLD,
AS WELL!
Graham:
THEN CONSIDER THIS
THE VOICE OF THE WORLD!
YOU'RE NOT!
YOU'RE JUST FORCING YOUR
OWN DISTORTED EGO ON OTHERS!
AND NOW I'M COMING FOR YOU!
TO CUT THAT TWISTED PART
OUT OF YOU!
WELL SAID, GUNDAM!
(Aggressive yell)
(Boom)
YOU SEE, HOWARD?
DARYL,
I'VE AVENGED YOU.
(Boom)
(Gasping)
GUNDAM.
(Alarm beeping)
(Struggling)
(Gasping)
THIS ISN'T THE END.
THE PLAN, NO MATTER WHAT,
THE PLAN CONTINUES.
(Wincing)
Tieria:
I HAVE TO AT LEAST
SAVE THE SOLAR REACTOR.
Feldt (gasps):
NADLEEH EJECTED ITS GN DRIVE.
TIERIA.
(Struggling to breath)
NOW I CAN FINALLY GO
TO WHERE YOU HAVE GONE,
LOCKON.
(Electrical buzzing)
(Gasping)
IT CAN'T BE.
THAT PILOT SOMA PERIES
IS ACTUALLY MARIE!
DID YOU KNOW THAT,
HALLELUJAH?
IF YOU'D KNOWN,
YOU WOULD NO LONGER FIGHT BACK.
YOU WOULD JUST DIE.
(Startled sigh)
DON'T WORRY, IT'S ALL RIGHT.
IT DOESN'T MATTER EITHER WAY.
(Chuckles)
I'LL BE GOING FIRST.
HALLELUJAH?
DOES THIS MEAN...
IT CAN'T BE.
(Sadly)
HALLELUJAH.
(Setsuna's voice reading letter)
MARINA ISMAIL.
BY THE TIME YOU READ THIS,
I WILL NO LONGER BE
IN THIS WORLD.
THE ERADICATION OF WAR
THROUGH THE USE OF ARMED FORCE.
ALL I KNEW HOW TO DO WAS FIGHT.
BUT CELESTIAL BEING
GAVE ME A REASON
WHY I SHOULD FIGHT.
LIKE THAT DAY I SAW THE GUNDAM.
I WANTED TO KNOW,
WHY WAS THE WORLD SO TWISTED?
WHERE DID THIS TWISTEDNESS
COME FROM?
HOW CAN PEOPLE BE SO WICKED
WITHOUT MEANING TO BE?
AND WHY DON'T THEY REALIZE
THEIR WICKEDNESS?
WHY ARE THERE THINGS THAT
BRING CHAOS TO SO MANY LIVES?
WHY DO PEOPLE RULE,
AND LET THEMSELVES BE RULED?
AND WHY DO THEY
HURT EACH OTHER?
AND WHY, DESPITE ALL THAT,
DO PEOPLE STILL WANT TO
LIVE THEIR LIVES?
I WAS JUST LOOKING FOR ANSWERS.
I THOUGHT THAT
IF I MET WITH YOU,
YOU'D GIVE ME THOSE ANSWERS.
BECAUSE YOU'RE LOOKING
FOR THE SAME THING,
ALONG A DIFFERENT PATH
FROM MINE.
FOR THE PATH WHERE PEOPLE CAN
UNDERSTAND EACH OTHER,
FOR THOSE ANSWERS.
SETSUNA...
I WAS LOOKING FOR ANSWERS,
TOGETHER WITH MY GUNDAM...
WITH... MY GUNDAM.
(Saji's voice reading letter)
LOUISE. I HAVEN'T WRITTEN
TO YOU IN A WHILE NOW.
IT'S BEEN TWO YEARS
SINCE YOU STOPPED WRITING BACK.
BUT I THOUGHT
I'D TRY ONE MORE TIME
SINCE I'VE GOT SOME REALLY
EXCITING NEWS
THAT I'VE WANTED TO TELL YOU.
BEGINNING THIS YEAR,
I'VE ACTUALLY STARTED
WORKING IN SPACE.
A LOT OF SAD THINGS
HAPPENED ALONG THE WAY,
BUT AT LEAST I WAS ABLE TO
MAKE ONE SMALL DREAM COME TRUE.
SO I WANT YOU TO LET ME MAKE
THE OTHER DREAM COME TRUE TOO.
I'LL BE WAITING, LOUISE.
WAITING IN SPACE.
HUH?
LOOK AT THAT.
IS THAT A TRAIL OF LIGHT
FROM GN PARTICLES?
WHOSE SHIP
COULD THAT BE?
I DON'T THINK
IT'S ONE OF THE FEDERATION'S.
WHAT?
THE PARTICLES
ARE A DIFFERENT COLOR.
HUH...
YEAH.
YOU'RE RIGHT.
(Thinking)
THAT LIGHT. YEAH.
THAT'S THE LIGHT
FROM A GUNDAM.
♪
Secretary General:
IT HAS BEEN ONE YEAR
SINCE THE UNITED NATIONS
WAS RENAMED
THE EARTH SPHERE FEDERATION.
WITH THE APPROVAL OF
ALL 328 MEMBER NATIONS
OF THE FEDERATION,
WE HEREBY DECLARE
THAT ALL NATIONAL ARMED FORCES
WILL BE DISSOLVED,
AND REFORMED
INTO A SINGLE MILITARY,
THE PEACEKEEPING FORCES OF
THE EARTH SPHERE FEDERATION.
(Applause)
Secretary General:
WHEN EVERY NATION'S ARMY
IS DISSOLVED,
AND OUR PEACEKEEPING
FORCES SERVE AS
THE ONLY MILITARY IN THE WORLD,
THEN THE WORLD WILL
HAVE ACHIEVED TRUE UNIFICATION.
OUR INTENTION IS TO PLAY
THE ROLE OF A GUIDEPOST
TOWARDS THAT GOAL AS WE
ALL PROCEED FORWARD TOGETHER!
Nena (off screen):
HAS THE WORLD FINALLY CHANGED,
MISTRESS?
Liu Mei (off screen):
WHO KNOWS?
Nena:
DO YOU NOT LIKE
THE CURRENT WORLD?
Liu Mei:
WELL, I'M STILL HOPEFUL
THAT THE WORLD CAN CHANGE.
(Gasping)
IT'S ABOUT TO BEGIN.
WATCH, INNOVATORS.
THE FUTURE OF HUMANITY...
(Growling)
HMPH.
♪
Ian:
SORRY YOU HAD TO COME
ALL THE WAY OUT HERE, MISS.
Liu Mei:
WHAT'S THE SITUATION?
WE JUST ROLLED OUT
THE FIRST ONE.
WE'RE SENDING IT OUT FOR TESTING
BEFORE WE USE IT IN BATTLE.
AND THE OTHER
MACHINES?
WE EXPECT TO ROLL THEM OUT
RIGHT ON SCHEDULE.
I'D LIKE TO SEE
THE FIRST GENERATION MACHINE
IF IT'S NOT
TOO MUCH OF A BOTHER.
HMM?
ROGER THAT!
(Gate opening)
(Gate clangs open)
Liu Mei:
THIS IS THE 0 GUNDAM.
THE FIRST WORKING MACHINE TO BE
EQUIPPED WITH A SOLAR REACTOR.
Ian:
WE ALREADY REMOVED
THE SOLAR REACTOR
AND INSTALLED IT
IN THE NEW MACHINE.
BUT EVEN THAT ONE
WASN'T A MATCH.
I REALLY DON'T KNOW
IF IT'S GOING TO
WORK WITH EXIA'S SOLAR REACTOR.
Liu Mei:
THE MACHINE
THAT WILL CHANGE THE WORLD.
THE DOUBLE 0 GUNDAM.