Saji:
WHAT DO YOU MEAN?!
WHY WON'T THE REGENERATION
TREATMENT WORK ON HER HAND?
WE FOUND ABNORMALITIES IN THE
STEM CELLS AROUND THE INJURY.
THE DOCTOR THINKS THERE MUST
HAVE BEEN SOMETHING ABOUT
THE GUNDAM'S BEAM WEAPON THAT
CAUSED THESE CELLULAR DEFECTS.
YOU...YOU MEAN SHE...
(Incoming message alert)
YOU CAN'T STAY HERE, SAJI.
YOU HAVE TO GO BACK HOME.
WAIT FOR ME IN SPACE.
I'LL CATCH UP TO YOU SOON.
IN SPACE.
(Sobbing)
LOUISE.
♪
UN Secretary‐General:
TO COUNTER THE REPEATED ACTS
OF IMMORAL TERRORISM
CARRIED OUT BY CELESTIAL BEING,
THE UNION,
THE HUMAN REFORM LEAGUE,
AND THE AEU WILL FORM
A MILITARY ALLIANCE.
THUS, MILITARY OPERATIONS,
UNDER UN SUPERVISION,
WILL BE CONDUCTED
FOR THE PURPOSE OF
DESTROYING CELESTIAL BEING!
(Applause)
THE THREE BLOCS HAVE
ANNOUNCED
A MILITARY ALLIANCE
TO BE CONTROLLED BY THE UN.
WITH THIS AGREEMENT,
THE LARGEST UN MILITARY FORCE
IN HISTORY IS BORN.
IT APPEARS THAT THINGS ARE
STILL PROGRESSING
ACCORDING TO THE SCRIPT
THAT CELESTIAL BEING
HAS WRITTEN FOR US.
THEN THESE RECENT RADICAL
INTERVENTIONS WERE DONE
TO CREATE A UNIFIED
UN MILITARY.
Shirin:
THAT SEEMS LIKE
A REASONABLE CONCLUSION.
Marina: (Thinking)
CELESTIAL BEING'S TRUE GOAL
WAS TO UNITE THE WORLD AS ONE.
REJECT FIGHTING WITH FIGHTING,
AND YOU WIN PEACE.
IS THIS THE WORLD
YOU WERE HOPING FOR, SETSUNA?
Lockon:
JUDGING BY THE REACTION,
WE'VE FINALLY CLEARED
THE FIRST STAGE OF THE PLAN.
THOUGH I'M UNEASY WITH THE FACT
THAT IT WAS THE TRINITYS'
ACTIONS THAT TRIGGERED IT.
BUT WE STILL HAVE A MYSTERY.
ABOUT WHAT?
THE TRINITYS INFLICTED
SERIOUS DAMAGE
TO THE MILITARY BASES
OF MANY OF THOSE COUNTRIES.
IN THEIR CONDITION,
EVEN IF THEY UNITED THEIR ARMIES
THEY COULDN'T DO ANYTHING
ABOUT THAT.
THE GENERAL PUBLIC WOULD
ONLY REACT WITH DISAPPOINTMENT.
THERE'S SOMETHING ELSE GOING ON.
TO BE HONEST, I'M UNEASY
ABOUT ALL OF THIS.
THERE'S THE FACT THAT
TEAM TRINITY ISN'T MENTIONED
ANYWHERE IN
VEDA'S INFORMATION.
NEVER MIND THE DISTURBING
REALIZATION
THAT VEDA'S DATA
HAS ACTUALLY BEEN ALTERED.
IT JUST MAKES ME UNEASY.
IS THAT SO?
(Beeping)
HMM.
Setsuna:
A CODED MESSAGE
FROM SUMERAGI LEE NORIEGA.
ALL MEISTERS ARE TO RETURN TO
PTOLEMAIOS WITH THEIR MACHINES.
Lockon:
OKAY, MISSION BRIEFING.
BACK TO SPACE, BOYS.
Lasse:
SO, THE QUESTION
IS WHAT DO WE DO NOW?
WE'LL SEE WHAT THE UN
DOES FIRST.
Ian:
YEAH, BUT I'M SURE
YOU'VE MADE A FORECAST, RIGHT?
IN ANY EVENT, WE SHOULD PREPARE
WHATEVER WE CAN
WHILE WE STILL HAVE TIME.
SINCE YOU ASKED,
IAN, WOULD YOU MIND TAKING LASSE
AND PICKING UP THE GN ARMS?
ROGER THAT!
NO WAY, YOU MEAN THE GN ARMS
HAVE BEEN ROLLED OUT?
WELL, JUST ONE OF THEM
FOR NOW.
THE REMAINING MEMBERS
WILL CONTINUE ON
AND HELP RETRIEVE THE GUNDAMS
THAT ARE COMING UP RIGHT NOW.
ROGER!
FINALLY, A CHANCE TO
DEPLOY THE GN ARMS.
THE CURRENT SITUATION IS
PRECARIOUS ENOUGH
THAT WE MAY
JUST NEED TO USE IT.
KATAGIRI,
ABOUT THAT ANALYSIS WE RAN ON
THE NEW MODEL GUNDAM'S
BEAM SABER...
WE HAVE MORE IMPORTANT
MATTERS RIGHT NOW.
WHY? WHAT'S HAPPENED?
APPARENTLY,
THERE'S A TRAITOR
IN THE CELESTIAL BEING
ORGANIZATION.
WAIT, DID YOU SAY "TRAITOR"?
YES.
AND THEY BROUGHT GIFTS.
SPECIFICALLY, THE SAME KIND OF
ENGINES THE GUNDAMS USE
AND SOME MOBILE SUITS
TO PUT THEM INTO.
WHAT, FOR REAL?
AND WE'RE TALKING
THIRTY MACHINES.
THAT'S THE REASON WHY THOSE GUYS
COULD MAKE THAT ANNOUNCEMENT.
Graham:
I SEE. NOW IT MAKES SENSE.
Katagiri:
THE PILOTS FOR THE MACHINES
THEY'RE GIVING US
WILL PROBABLY BE CHOSEN FROM
AMONG THE OVER FLAGS MEMBERS.
AND OF COURSE,
YOU'D BE IN CHARGE.
I'LL HAVE TO REFUSE THAT.
HUH?
I WILL DEFEAT THE GUNDAMS
WITH A FLAG.
I STOOD OVER HOWARD MASON'S
GRAVE AND MADE A VOW.
Daryl:
BUT CAPTAIN! AGAINST A GUNDAM,
THE FLAG'S PERFORMANCE‐‐
A MAN CANNOT GO BACK ON HIS VOW!
(Sighs)
OKAY, THEN.
SO THIS IS THE GUNDAM'S
MAIN ENGINE.
ACCORDING TO OUR DATA
THE ENGINE IS OFFICIALLY
CALLED A "GN DRIVE".
A GN DRIVE.
THE HUMAN REFORM LEAGUE WAS
GIVEN TEN OF THESE GN DRIVES.
COLONEL,
YOU'LL BE IN CHARGE OF
SELECTING THE PILOTS.
YES, SIR.
COLONEL, PERMIT ME TO PILOT
ONE OF THE NEW MODELS.
LIEUTENANT.
OF COURSE YOU'LL BE PERMITTED.
COMMANDER.
I HEAR THAT THE YOUNG
LIEUTENANT'S QUANTUM BRAIN WAVES
HAVE A DISABLING EFFECT UPON
THE PILOT OF THE WINGED GUNDAM.
WE MUST MAKE USE OF
THAT ADVANTAGE.
I WILL DO MY BEST, SIR!
Commander:
WE EXPECT NOTHING LESS.
Peries:
YES, SIR!
FOR PILOT CANDIDATES,
WE'LL ASSEMBLE THE TOP GUNS
FROM THE AEU MEMBER NATIONS.
THE QUESTION IS WHETHER OR NOT
I SHOULD INCLUDE HIM.
(Doorbell rings)
HMM?
GOOD EVENING, COLONEL!
IT IS I, PATRICK COLASOUR!
WHAT ARE YOU DOING HERE,
LIEUTENANT?
IT'S SIMPLE COLONEL, I WANTED TO
ASK YOU OUT FOR DINNER.
(Sigh)
LIEUTENANT, THE WORLD IS
ABOUT TO UNDERGO
A REFORMATION
THAT WILL CHANGE EVERYTHING.
DOESN'T THE THOUGHT OF SOMETHING
LIKE THAT GIVE YOU ANY PAUSE?
NOPE! NOT AT ALL!
(Sigh)
YOU'RE JUST LIKE A BIG KID.
WHAT DO YOU MEAN?
WAIT HERE. I'LL GET READY.
(Excited giggle)
OH BOY!
JNN AGAIN?
TELL THEM I HAVE NO INTENTION
OF ANSWERING
ANY QUESTIONS ABOUT THAT.
Secreatary:
VERY GOOD, SIR.
(Sigh)
MUST BE HARD
BEING SO POPULAR.
DON'T MOCK ME.
RIGHT THEN.
I HEAR DISTRIBUTION
OF THE MACHINES
IS GOING ACCORDING TO PLAN.
MISTER LAGUNA HARVEY,
IF I'M PAID FOR A JOB,
I MAKE SURE IT GETS DONE.
SO, WHY ARE YOU HERE?
A SIMPLE REQUEST,
I'LL GET RIGHT TO THE POINT.
I'D LIKE TO GET MY HANDS ON
ONE OF THOSE NEW MODEL MACHINES
THAT WE'RE NOW DISTRIBUTING.
(Unimpressed grunt)
DON'T BE RIDICULOUS, MAN.
WELL THEN I'D LIKE YOU TO
USE YOUR INFLUENCE TO
GET ME ASSIGNED
TO SOMEONE'S MILITARY,
THE UNION OR THE AEU,
IT DOESN'T REALLY MATTER TO ME.
WEREN'T YOU ASSIGNED TO
THE FRENCH FOREIGN LEGION
OR SOMETHING?
UNDER THE NAME OF
LIEUTENANT GARY BIAGGI.
I'VE HEARD A LOT ABOUT
YOUR GREAT INSTINCTS.
BUT WHY DO YOU WANT TO PILOT
ONE OF THOSE THINGS SO BADLY?
THERE'S SOMEONE
I OWE A LITTLE PAYBACK TO,
THREE TIMES OVER NOW.
AND I HAVE
THIS FEELING IN MY GUT
THAT TELLS ME MERCENARIES
AREN'T GOING TO BE
THAT NECESSARY
IN THE NEAR FUTURE.
SO, I JUST WANT TO GO
WHERE I CAN FIGHT.
THAT ABOUT SUMS IT UP.
HOW MUCH DO YOU KNOW EXACTLY?
LIKE I SAID,
IT'S ONLY A GUT FEELING!
PLEASE, THINK IT OVER,
MR. HARVEY.
DAMN IT.
ALL BECAUSE OF THOSE
CELESTIAL WHATYOUMALLITS.
(Disappointed sigh)
I CAN'T GET AN INTERVIEW.
SO WHAT DO I DO NOW?
(Car drives by)
HUH?
FUNNY, THEY TOLD ME
THE PRESIDENT WAS IN A MEETING.
HMM.
UH, HELLO?
HOW MAY I HELP YOU, MISS?
I'M A SPECIAL CORRESPONDENT
FROM JNN
AND I'D LIKE TO ASK YOU
A COUPLE OF QUESTIONS,
IF THAT'S
ALL RIGHT WITH YOU?
YOU'RE A REPORTER FROM JNN?
OH, I DON'T MIND. BUT SEE,
I AM IN A BIT OF A HURRY.
COULD YOU ASK THEM IN THE CAR?
WELL, I DON'T KNOW
ABOUT THAT.
Al‐Saachez:
WELL, I GUESS
YOU'D RATHER NOT.
(Grunts)
OKAY, I'LL TAKE YOU UP ON THAT.
Al‐Saachez:
MISS KINUE CROSSROAD.
HOW REFRESHING. NICE TO SEE A
BEAUTIFUL REPORTER FOR A CHANGE.
THANK YOU.
SO, WHAT DID YOU WANT
TO ASK ME ANYWAY?
I APOLOGIZE
IF I'M WRONG ABOUT THIS,
BUT MR. BIAGGI, WERE YOU JUST
IN A MEETING WITH LAGUNA HARVEY,
THE PRESIDENT OF
THE TRAIN CORPORATION?
YES. I DID MEET WITH HIM.
WHAT DID THE
TWO OF YOU DISCUSS?
I GUESS YOU COULD SAY
I WORK IN DISTRIBUTION.
I WAS REPORTING TO
THE PRESIDENT
TO CONFIRM THE DISTRIBUTION
OF CERTAIN GOODS.
DIRECTLY TO THE PRESIDENT?
YES.
ARE THESE GOODS FOR
PRIVATE USE?
YES. PRIVATE USE.
IF YOU DON'T MIND, COULD YOU
PLEASE TELL ME EXACTLY
WHAT KIND OF PRIVATE GOODS
WE'RE TALKING ABOUT HERE?
(Chuckles)
GN DRIVES.
GN DRIVES FOR...
ARE THEY LIKE COMPONENTS
FOR LINEAR TRAINS OR SOMETHING?
NO. THEY'RE ENGINES
FOR POWERING MOBILE SUITS.
DID YOU SAY MOBILE SUITS?
GUNDAMS, IN FACT.
(Gasps)
YOU'VE HEARD OF THEM.
THE ONES POSSESSED BY
CELESTIAL BEING.
ONE OF THEIR PILOTS IS
AN EX‐CHILD SOLDIER FROM KRUGIS.
I MEAN THOSE GUNDAMS.
A CHILD SOLDIER
FROM KRUGIS?
JUST A PUNK, REALLY.
SOMEONE ABDUCTED HIM,
BRAINWASHED HIM,
TRAINED HIM TO FIGHT
AND ESSENTIALLY MOLDED HIM
INTO A GUERILLA SOLDIER.
I'M THE ONE WHO DID ALL THAT.
(Scared gasp)
WHO... WHO ARE YOU?
I'M A WARMONGER.
I CAN'T HELP IT,
I LOVE EVERYTHING ABOUT WAR.
I'M THE VERY WORST
KIND OF PERSON,
SOMEONE WHO LIVES AND DIES
FOR HUMANITY'S
MOST PRIMITIVE IMPULSE.
(Terrified gasp)
GUESS SHE'S ON ANOTHER
BUSINESS TRIP.
Laguna:
IT'S ME.
I TOOK CARE OF THAT PESKY RAT
THAT WAS SCURRYING AROUND.
THAT WASN'T NECESSARY.
I THINK
IT'LL BE GOOD PROPAGANDA,
HELP US GET MORE PUBLIC SUPPORT
AND ALL THAT.
YOU KNOW, YOU'RE A HARD MAN
TO FIGURE OUT.
(Chuckles)
LOUISE.
(Painful gasping)
FATHER.
SA... SAJI.
(Struggling gasps)
(Heavy rain)
Ribbons:
MASTER ALEJANDRO,
I REALLY DON'T SEE
THE NEED FOR YOU
TO ACCOMPANY ME IN PERSON.
Alejandro:
WELL, THIS IS INFORMATION YOU
WENT OUT OF YOUR WAY TO OBTAIN.
I'D LIKE TO SEE IT
WITH MY OWN EYES.
BESIDES, THIS HAS BEEN AN
ARDENT WISH OF THE CORNER FAMILY
FOR A VERY LONG TIME.
MASTER ALEJANDRO, OR,
YOUR WHOLE FAMILY...
I TAKE IT YOU'VE BEEN PLANNING
TO INTERFERE WITH THIS PROJECT
FOR MANY GENERATIONS.
INDEED WE HAVE.
BUT AS LONG AS VEDA WAS
UP AND RUNNING,
THERE WAS NOTHING
WE COULD REALLY DO ABOUT IT.
AND THEN ONE DAY,
PURELY BY CHANCE,
AN ANGEL DESCENDED BEFORE ME.
I'M TALKING ABOUT YOU,
RIBBONS ALMARK.
I WILL REPAY YOU FOR TAKING ME
IN AND TREATING ME SO WELL.
BUT I DIDN'T EXPECT YOU TO FIND
THE LOCATION
OF THE MAIN SYSTEM.
SORRY, I DIDN'T THINK IT WOULD
TAKE THAT LONG TO TRACE IT.
DON'T APOLOGIZE.
YOU TRULY ARE MY ANGEL.
Nena:
AFTER MAKING US
WORK LIKE, NONSTOP,
HOW COULD THEY SUDDENLY CUT OFF
CONTACT WITH US?
I DON'T KNOW
WHY YOU'RE ASKING ME, NENA.
I'M NO GOOD AT THINKING ABOUT
COMPLICATED STUFF LIKE THAT.
YEAH, YOU'RE THE
SIMPLE TYPE ALRIGHT!
HEY, STOP
MAKING FUN OF ME!
MORON! MORON!
DAMN YOU, HARO!
YOU WANT TO GET SLICED UP?!
MICHAEL!
HARO'S AN INVALUABLE ASSET
TO TEAM TRINITY.
UH, I WAS JOKING JOHANN,
JUST JOKING!
WE'VE JUST RECEIVED
A MISSION PLAN FROM LAGUNA.
IT'S THE SAME THING AS USUAL.
THE MISSION WILL COMMENCE
IN THREE DAYS.
IT'S ABOUT TIME!
Liu‐Mei:
FINALLY, I'VE FOUND YOU.
(Gasp)
Nena:
BUT HOW?! HOW'D YOU GET PAST
OUR SECURITY?!
THAT DOESN'T MATTER!
NOW THAT SHE'S FOUND US
AND SEEN THE PLACE
WE CAN'T LET HER
GET OUT OF HERE ALIVE!
STAND DOWN, MICHAEL.
I KNOW WHO SHE IS.
I RECALL READING ABOUT HER
IN THE MATERIAL FROM VEDA.
I AM HONORED THAT YOU REMEMBERED
SOMEONE LIKE ME.
MY NAME IS WANG LIU MEI.
I'M AN UNDERCOVER AGENT
FOR CELESTIAL BEING.
AND THIS IS MY PARTNER IN CRIME,
HONG LONG.
OH, HE'S TOTALLY YUMMY.
WHAT, HIM?!
GIVEN THE FACT
YOU ACTUALLY FOUND THIS PLACE,
YOUR SKILLS
ARE FORMIDABLE INDEED.
WELL THEN, HOW CAN THE THREE
OF US BE OF SERVICE TO YOU?
I SIMPLY DROPPED IN
TO SAY HELLO.
HMM?
TEAM TRINITY ARE MEMBERS OF
CELESTIAL BEING AND SO ARE WE.
AS AN AGENT I FEEL I SHOULD DO
MY BEST TO AID AND ASSIST YOU.
IT IS ONLY NATURAL.
ARE YOU KIDDING ME?!
IN CASE YOU FORGOT, YOUR GUNDAMS
LAUNCHED AN ATTACK ON US!
YES, I HAVE ALREADY HEARD
ABOUT THE INCIDENT.
BUT YOU SHOULD KNOW,
WE'RE NOT NECESSARILY ON THE
SIDE OF THOSE WHO ATTACKED YOU.
HANG ON. ARE YOU SAYING THAT
YOU'RE NEUTRAL?
OH NO, I AM SIMPLY
A FOLLOWER OF THE ORIGINAL IDEAS
THAT AEOLIA SCHENBERG ADVOCATED.
AND THAT'S ALL, NOTHING MORE,
AND NOTHING LESS.
I SEE, SO THAT'S WHAT
THIS IS ABOUT.
Liu‐Mei:
INDEED.
HUH?
HMM?
I UNDERSTAND.
WANG LIU MEI,
SHOULD IT BECOME NECESSARY,
I WILL BE COUNTING ON
YOUR FULL SUPPORT.
AS YOU WISH.
AND WHAT ABOUT
OUR LOCATION?
I PROMISE I WILL NOT TELL THEM
ABOUT THIS PLACE.
GOOD BYE.
(Door closes)
ARE YOU SURE, JOHANN?
SHOULD WE JUST LET THEM LEAVE?
OH, I THINK WE'LL BE FINE.
BESIDES, THE MORE CARDS
WE HAVE TO PLAY,
THE BETTER OFF WE ARE.
SHE WAS PRETTY!
SHUT UP!
SOMEONE'S JEALOUS!
IS THIS THE RIGHT THING TO DO,
MISTRESS?
CELESTIAL BEING
IS HOSTILE TOWARDS THEM.
THAT DOESN'T MATTER.
WHAT MATTERS IS THAT
TEAM TRINITY
HAS TRIGGERED
THE WORLD'S REFORMATION.
DO YOU TRULY DISLIKE THE CURRENT
WORLD THAT MUCH, MISTRESS?
YES. AND IF IT DOESN'T CHANGE,
I WOULDN'T MIND AT ALL
IF THIS WORLD
WAS SMASHED TO PIECES.
Christina:
EXIA HAS DOCKED.
WHAT'S OUR SITUATION?
NOTHING'S REALLY
CHANGED AS OF YET.
Allelujah:
THE TRINITYS HAVE BEEN
PRETTY QUIET.
I AM GUILTY OF
DISOBEYING ORDERS.
REALLY, WHEN DID YOU DO THAT?
BUT I...
AH!
LOOK, JUST ACCEPT IT.
HMM.
DID SOMETHING HAPPEN?
NOT AT ALL.
Christina:
MISS SUMERAGI!
TEAM TRINITY APPEARS TO BE
ON THE MOVE.
Lockon:
NOW WHAT?
ALRIGHT, WHAT'S
THEIR ATTACK TARGET, FELDT?
THERE'S AN HRL BASE
ON THEIR ROUTE.
IT'S THE GUANGZHOU MILITARY
DISTRICT.
Announcer:
MESSAGE FOR ALL PERSONNEL FROM
THE OBSERVATION TEAM:
THREE MOBILE SUITS
BELIEVED TO BE
THE NEW MODEL GUNDAMS
ARE APPROACHING
FROM DIRECTION S‐9788.
IT IS BELIEVED THEY INTEND TO
PERFORM AN ARMED
INTERVENTION.
I'M STILL PISSED ABOUT
WHAT HAPPENED THE OTHER DAY!
Michael:
I'M GOING TO REALLY CUT LOOSE!
IS THAT OKAY, JOHANN?
Johann:
SEEMS FINE
ACCORDING TO THE PLAN.
NOW THAT'S MORE LIKE IT!
(Growls)
Michael:
HERE I GO!
Soldier #1:
(Gasps)
THERE'S ONE MORE COMING!
Nena:
HIT 'EM HARD!
Soldier #2:
DON'T HESITATE!
CONCENTRATE YOUR FIRE!
SHOOTING FROM BEHIND ISN'T FAIR!
DON'T MESS WITH US,
YOU LITTLE PESTS!
Soldier #3:
THOSE DAMN DEMONS!
LET'S WRAP THIS MISSION UP.
PREPARE FOR DOCKING.
ROGER!
The Trinitys:
(Startled yell)
WHAT WAS THAT?!
IS IT THE EXIA AGAIN?!
Johann:
NO, IT ISN'T.
A FORMATION OF TEN?
THOSE AREN'T GUNDAMS!
Michael:
WHAT'S GOING ON HERE?!
Nena:
AND THEY'RE EMITTING
GN PARTICLES!
COULD IT BE THEY'RE MEMBERS
OF CELESTIAL BEING TOO?!
Sergei:
CHOBU GN‐X TEAM,
COMMENCE OFFENSIVE MANEUVERS.
THESE BABIES ARE PRECIOUS.
DON'T LET THEM GET WRECKED!
ATTACK!
Nena:
(Painful yelps)
WHAT IS WITH THEIR MOBILITY?!
WHAT SUPERB PERFORMANCE!
THIS MACHINE IS AMAZING!
(Crash)
WHAT DO YOU THINK YOU'RE DOING?!
THE DAYS OF FEARING GUNDAMS
HAVE COME TO AN END!
Nena:
OH, YEAH?!
I MISSED!
(Aggressive yell)
(Metal crashing)
(Screams)
Michael:
NENA!
I SHALL BE YOUR NEXT OPPONENT!
THAT'S YOUR FUNERAL!
Michael:
FANGS!
WHAT THE HELL?!
THIS MACHINE CAN KEEP UP
WITH MY REACTION SPEED.
THIS IS THE POWER OF A GUNDAM!
STOP TRASHING MY FANGS!
WE'RE LEAVING!
JOHANN!
NO ARGUING FROM YOU!
ARGH!
Peries:
STOP!
Sergei:
THAT'S ENOUGH FOR TODAY!
BUT WHY, COLONEL?!
LOOK DOWN AT THE BASE.
(Soldiers cheering)
WHY ARE THEY CHEERING?
THEY TOOK SO MUCH DAMAGE
IN THE FIGHT.
I GUESS THIS IS
YOUR FIRST TASTE,
ISN'T IT, LIEUTENANT?
THIS IS THE SWEET TASTE
OF VICTORY.
(Soldiers cheering)
Feldt:
THE TRINITYS SEEM TO HAVE LEFT
THE COMBAT AIRSPACE.
DID THEY ACTUALLY
RETREAT?
YEAH,
WHAT HAPPENED?!
THE HUMAN REFORM LEAGUE DEPLOYED
A TEAM OF MOBILE SUITS
EQUIPPED WITH SOLAR REACTORS.
SOLAR REACTORS.
BUT THAT'S...
THE INFORMATION MUST HAVE BEEN
TAKEN FROM VEDA.
FROM NOW ON, IT'S GOING TO BE
LIKE GUNDAM FIGHTING GUNDAM.
GUNDAMS FIGHTING.
ALREADY, THE WORLD HAS
CHANGED SO MUCH.
AFTER ALL THIS, WHAT COULD
POSSIBLY BE COMING NEXT?
Ribbons:
MASTER ALEJANDRO,
THIS WAY, PLEASE.
(Door unlocks)
(Gasps)
SO THIS IS VEDA!
THIS IS AEOLIA SCHENBERG!
AND THE SYSTEM THAT IS
THE HEART OF CELESTIAL BEING!
♪
Narrator:
THE NEW MODEL MOBILE SUITS SHOW
THE GUNDAMS THEIR CLAWS.
IS THIS THE CONDEMNATION
OF THOSE
WHO DREAMED OF
ERADICATING WARFARE?
NEXT EPISODE:
"PATH OF DESTRUCTION".
THIS IS THE WORLD'S
RESPONSE.