THIS CELESTIAL
WHATCHAMACALLIT...
IS TERRIBLE FOR BUSINESS.
IF FOLKS HERE CAN'T COLLECT
THESE ROCKS,
THIS NATION'S
ECONOMY WILL GO BUST...
CARE TO GUESS HOW MANY
COUNTRIES AND INDUSTRIES
WILL BE AFFECTED BY THAT?
AS LONG AS THEY CAN
STOP WAR THEY DON'T REALLY
CARE ABOUT WHAT HAPPENS TO
THE PEOPLE ON THE BOTTOM.
BOSS! YOU GOT A CALL
FROM THE PMC TRUST.
HELLO, ALI AL‐SAACHEZ HERE.
SO YOU SENT US ALL THE
WAY OUT HERE AND THEN
YOU JUST
CANCEL THE CONTRACT?
MERCENARIES MAKE THEIR
LIVING BY FIGHTING!
KEEP THIS UP AND
MORALIA'S GOING TO COLLAPSE!
GOT IT, WE'LL RETURN TO
HEADQUARTERS.
SOMETHING WRONG?
(Chuckles)
THE BIG SHOTS AT THE
AEU ARE WISING UP.
THEY'RE FINALLY GETTING
OFF THEIR BUTTS
AND DOING SOMETHING.
SO, DO YOU INTEND
TO SEND THE ARMY
TO MORALIA NO MATTER WHAT?
AT THE EUROPEAN SUMMIT
THE OTHER DAY,
WE CONFIRMED THAT MORALIA'S
PMC'S ARE NECESSARY
FOR OUR SPACE
DEVELOPMENT PROJECTS.
NO MATTER HOW BAD ITS
FINANCIAL PROBLEMS
SEEM TO BE, IF WE
KEEP SUPPORTING MORALIA,
CELESTIAL BEING WILL BE‐‐
AND THAT IS PRECISELY WHY
WE MUST SEND THE MILITARY.
BUT LET'S NOT BE TOO RASH,
THINK OF THE
PUBLIC OPINION BACKLASH
IF WE SEND OUR SOLDIERS
ONTO FOREIGN SOIL.
WE SHOULDN'T BE WORRYING ABOUT
WHAT HAPPENED
THREE CENTURIES AGO,
WE'RE TRYING TO DO WHAT'S
BEST FOR THE AEU OF TODAY.
WE SHOULD LEAVE THE
ACTUAL COLONY DEVELOPMENT
TO THE UNION AND THE HRL.
AFTER ALL THEY
WOULDN'T BE ABLE TO DO IT
WITHOUT OUR GENEROUS
FINANCIAL SUPPORT.
THAT MAY WORK FOR
NATIONS LIKE YOURS
THAT POSSESS TREMENDOUS
WEALTH...
BUT I'M AFRAID THE
SITUATION
IS QUITE A BIT
DIFFERENT FOR MY COUNTRY.
IS YOUR COUNTRY
THAT DESPERATE
TO SELL ALL THOSE WEAPONS
YOU'VE BEEN DEVELOPING?
MOVING INTO SPACE
WITHOUT A STRONG MILITARY
WILL BE IMPOSSIBLE.
IF WE GIVE UP CONTROL OF SPACE
TO THE UNION AND THE HUMAN
REFORM LEAGUE,
THE FINAL FRONTIER
WILL BE LOST TO US.
UNDOUBTEDLY.
WE CANNOT AFFORD
TO FALL
ANY FURTHER BEHIND
IN THE SPACE
DEVELOPMENT RACE.
FORCES MUST BE
DEPLOYED TO MORALIA,
BUT ONLY BY COUNTRIES THAT
AGREE TO DO SO.
IF THAT'S THE WAY IT IS...
HOWEVER...
WE SHALL REQUIRE THE CONSENSUS
OF ALL
THE AEU MEMBER NATIONS.
IN EFFECT...
WE SHALL BE THE WHITE
KNIGHT WHO SAVES MORALIA.
♪
GN DRIVE LINKAGE SATISFACTORY.
GN PARTICLE CHARGE STATUS:
CURRENTLY 75 PERCENT.
DISPERSAL STATUS,
HOLDING STEADY AT FORTY PERCENT.
THERE ARE CURRENTLY NO
UNKNOWNS WITHIN VISUAL RANGE.
YOU KNOW...
IT'S BEEN JUST OVER
A WEEK, YOU GUYS.
WHAT ARE YOU TALKING ABOUT?
I MEAN ALLELUJAH!
THERE'S NOTHING WRONG
WITH SAVING LIVES.
(Wincing)
WHERE DID THIS
HEADACHE COME FROM?!
(Yelling in pain)
WHO... WAS THAT...?
HI.
SO, IS MY SENTENCE UP?
FROM THE SOUNDS OF IT...
YOU DON'T FEEL SORRY ABOUT
YOUR ACTIONS, DO YOU?
I GUESS YOU'RE RIGHT.
ALLELUJAH HAPTISM.
YOU'RE NOT WORTHY OF
BEING A GUNDAM MEISTER.
WHAT, YOU WANT TO
PULL ME OFF KYRIOS?
THAT'S RIGHT.
AT LEAST THAT'S
WHAT I'D LIKE TO DO.
BUT WE ACTUALLY CAN'T
AFFORD TO DO IT RIGHT NOW.
WE HAVE A TASK
THAT WILL
REQUIRE YOUR
ABILITIES AGAIN.
MISS SUMERAGI.
WE HAVE RECEIVED INFORMATION
THAT THE PRESIDENT OF THE
MORALIAN REPUBLIC
IS HAVING
CLANDESTINE MEETINGS WITH
THE FOREIGN MINISTERS OF
THE MAJOR AEU NATIONS.
MORALIA?
THE PMC'S, RIGHT?
WE CAN CONSIDER
THESE ACTIONS
TO BE A DIRECT
CHALLENGE TO US.
THIS WILL BE
A HARD MISSION.
WE'LL BE HEADING DOWN TO THE
SURFACE TO PROVIDE BACK UP.
ALLELUJAH, YOU'RE
RELEASED FROM CONFINEMENT.
BOTH OF YOU ARE GOING, SO
PREPARE FOR AN IMMEDIATE LAUNCH.
ROGER THAT.
WE'VE CONDUCTED A THOROUGH
PHYSICAL EXAMINATION
OF THE LIEUTENANT, BUT
WE'VE FOUND NO PROBLEMS.
THE NUMBERS INDICATE HER
BRAIN'S SYNAPTIC NERVE
IMPULSES AND GLIAL CELLS
ARE ALL AT NORMAL LEVELS.
I SEE. THEN WHY DID THE
LIEUTENANT
SUDDENLY
LOSE CONTROL LIKE THAT?
WE ANALYZED HER TAOZI'S
MISSION RECORDER AND DETECTED
ABNORMALITIES IN HER QUANTUM
BRAIN WAVES.
ORDINARILY,
THIS SHOULD BE IMPOSSIBLE.
WE COULD BE LOOKING AT AN
EXTERNAL INFLUENCE.
EXTERNAL INFLUENCE?
IF THAT'S SO, THEN
THE ONLY KIND OF INDIVIDUAL
WHO COULD CAUSE THIS REACTION
WOULD BE SOMEONE
LIKE THE LIEUTENANT,
WITH ENHANCED GLIAL CELLS
AND USING QUANTUM BRAIN WAVES.
SOMEONE ELSE LIKE
HER WAS OUT THERE?
WELL, I'M JUST SAYING IT
MIGHT BE A POSSIBILITY.
HOW DO WE
DEAL WITH THIS?
WE'VE MODIFIED
THE LIEUTENANT'S SUIT
SO IT BLOCKS QUANTUM
BRAIN WAVES.
THIS WON'T HAPPEN AGAIN.
IS IT THAT
IMPORTANT TO YOU
TO HAVE THE LIEUTENANT
OUT ON THE BATTLEFIELD?
IF THIS CELESTIAL BEING
ORGANIZATION
HAD NEVER
APPEARED ON THE SCENE...
OUR RESEARCH HERE...
WOULDN'T HAVE BEEN
EXPOSED TO THE WORLD.
Sergei:
IT ALWAYS LEADS
BACK TO THAT GROUP.
TECHNICAL ASSISTANCE WITH
SOLAR POWER GENERATION?
YES, WE DESPERATELY NEED
ASSISTANCE IN THAT MATTER.
HMM... I REALLY WISH
OUR NATION COULD HELP
WITH THIS DILEMMA
YOU'RE FACING, HOWEVER...
YOUR COUNTRY IS VERY
UNSTABLE RIGHT NOW.
WITHOUT A GUARANTEE THAT OUR
TECHNICIANS WOULD BE SAFE,
IT'S UNLIKELY WE'D RECEIVE
THE CONSENT OF THE ASSEMBLY.
BESIDES...
SINCE THE AEU'S ELEVATOR
ISN'T FULLY OPERATIONAL,
I DON'T KNOW IF
WE'D EVEN HAVE
THE TECHNICIANS
TO SEND ELSEWHERE.
HOW UNFORTUNATE.
THOUGH I'LL MAKE
EVERY EFFORT TO ENSURE
THAT AZADISTAN CONTINUES
TO RECEIVE FOOD AID.
THANK YOU FOR THAT.
TO PROTECT HER COUNTRY,
A YOUNG
PRINCESS ENTERS
THE UNFAMILIAR
WORLD OF FOREIGN POLICY.
I FEEL SORRY FOR HER...
BUT THESE ARE
SERIOUS MATTERS
AND WE'RE NOT RUNNING
A CHARITY.
I GUESS IT'S ALL
UP TO MORALIA NOW.
THAT'S GOOD TIMING!
MY SISTER MADE TOO MUCH
STEWED CHICKEN
AND WE CAN'T FINISH IT.
I WAS WONDERING IF
YOU'D LIKE SOME.
IT'S STILL WARM.
I'M ON MY WAY OUT.
OH.
I SEE.
THAT WAS A CLOSE CALL.
OH, AT THE STATION.
YEAH, THAT'S FOR SURE.
WHO WOULD HAVE THOUGHT
CELESTIAL BEING
WOULD SHOW UP
AND RESCUE US?
I NEVER IMAGINED THAT.
NEITHER DID I.
HUH?
Feldt:
THE MORALIAN REPUBLIC.
FOUNDED IN 2284,
IT IS A SMALL COUNTRY
SITUATED IN SOUTHERN EUROPE.
THE POPULATION IS
A RELATIVELY LOW 180,000,
BUT THERE ARE MORE THAN
THREE MILLION
FOREIGN WORKERS
RESIDING WITHIN ITS BORDERS.
PMC'S ACCOUNT
FOR TWENTY PERCENT
OF THE ROUGHLY FOUR THOUSAND
PRIVATE COMPANIES.
PMC STANDS FOR
PRIVATE MILITARY COMPANY.
THESE CONTRACTORS DEAL IN
MERCENARY DEPLOYMENTS,
THE TRAINING OF SOLDIERS,
WEAPONS DEVELOPMENT,
TRANSPORT AND LOGISTICAL
SUPPORT,
ALL BASED ON BUSINESS MODELS
FOR PROFIT.
YOU WORK WAY
TOO MUCH, FELDT.
JUST DOING MY DUTY.
MISS SUMERAGI,
MORALIA HAS DEVELOPED
BY INVITING IN THE PRIVATE
MILITARY COMPANIES
AND THEN GIVING THEM
FAVORABLE TREATMENT, RIGHT?
SO WHY WAS IT NEVER CONSIDERED
ONE OF OUR TARGETS UNTIL NOW?
IF WARS AROUND THE WORLD
DIMINISHED IN NUMBER...
THEN THEIR BUSINESS WOULDN'T
BE PROFITABLE ANYMORE.
IT WOULD'VE BEEN NICE
IF THEY ENDED UP
SELF‐DESTRUCTING ON
THEIR OWN.
SO, THE WORD IS...
MORALIA'S SPOILING FOR A
FIGHT WITH CELESTIAL BEING.
AND THE AEU HAS DECIDED
TO BACK THEM UP.
IF THEY WANT TO COMPLETE THEIR
SOLAR POWER GENERATION SYSTEM
AND MOVE ONTO SPACE
COLONY DEVELOPMENT...
THEN THE MANPOWER
AND TECHNOLOGY OF THE PMC'S
ARE CRITICAL
TO THEIR WHOLE PLAN.
AND ON THE OTHER HAND
THERE'S MORALIA,
WHICH JUST WANTS TO
REVIVE ITS FAILING ECONOMY.
EVEN IF THEIR COUNTRY DOES
BECOME A BATTLEFIELD,
THEY STILL NEED
BACKUP FROM THE AEU.
YOU KNOW...
IF THEY'RE LUCKY
THEY MIGHT EVEN CAPTURE
ONE OF THOSE MACHINES....
A GUNDAM.
(Chuckles)
WELL THEN, I GUESS
WE'LL JUST HAVE TO
HAND THIS ONE OVER TO THE
SO‐CALLED ACE OF THE AEU.
Patrick:
YA‐HOOO!
THIS IS THE MORALIAN
AIR FORCE BASE.
YOU HAVE PERMISSION TO LAND.
PLEASE USE RUNWAY
NUMBER SEVEN.
(Startled shouting)
WHAT WAS THAT FOR?!
YO! I'M THE ACE OF THE AEU,
PATRICK COLASOUR!
MEMBERS OF THE MORALIAN AIR
FORCE, I'M HERE TO HELP.
MAN... WHAT A BIG MOUTH!
DON'T KEEP ME WAITING,
GUNDAM!
I'M GOING TO TEAR YOU
INTO LITTLE PIECES!
MORALIA AND THE AEU ON A
JOINT MILITARY EXERCISE?
Hong‐Long:
THE AEU SENT A FULL REGIMENT
OF MOBILE SUITS
AND THE PMC TRUST,
WHO, AS I'M SURE YOU REALIZE,
IS AN ALLIANCE OF MORALIA'S
PRIVATE MILITARY COMPANIES,
IS ALSO TAKING PART
IN THE EXERCISE.
ADDING ALL THE
MOBILE SUITS TOGETHER,
IT'S ESTIMATED THEY HAVE
OVER 130 MACHINES.
A FULL‐SCALE MISSION.
THEY'VE NO CHOICE...
THE WORLD WILL HAVE TO TAKE
NOTICE OF CELESTIAL BEING NOW.
MISS SUMERAGI!
WE AREN'T LEAVING FOR MORALIA
UNTIL TOMORROW,
SO CAN WE PLEASE
HAVE SOME TIME OFF UNTIL THEN?
IS THAT
WHAT YOU WANT?
UH‐HUH!
WELL,
OKAY THEN!
AWESOME!
LET'S GO SHOPPING, FELDT!
I STILL NEED TO ANALYZE
THE MISSION PLAN.
COME ON! LET'S JUST GO!
THE MORE BATTLES WE HAVE
THE MORE INFLATION
IS GOING TO SKYROCKET!
IF WE WANT SOMETHING,
WE SHOULD BE BUYING IT NOW!
BUT THE DATA...
ALL RIGHT THEN, MISS SUMERAGI!
WE'RE LEAVING NOW!
BUT THE
ANALYSIS...
IT'LL BE JUST FINE.
WELL!
NOW TO FIND A DRINK!
♪
HEY! SETSUNA,
IT'S BEEN A LONG TIME!
AH, IAN VASHTI.
I HAVE SOME THINGS I WANTED
TO BRING TO YOU GUYS
AS SOON AS POSSIBLE.
HE BROUGHT OUT A COUPLE
OF SURPRISES FOR US!
PRESENTS! PRESENTS!
I'VE ALREADY EQUIPPED THE
DYNAMES OVER THERE
WITH ITS
ADDITIONAL WEAPONRY.
AND YOURS...
IS RIGHT OVER HERE.
THE GN BLADES ARE MADE
EXCLUSIVELY FOR THE EXIA.
THEY EMIT THE SAME
SUPER‐COMPRESSED PARTICLES
AS THE GN SWORD.
THEY'LL EASILY CUT THROUGH
THREE‐METER‐THICK
E‐CARBON PLATE.
WELL. ARE YOU IMPRESSED?
EXIA'S GN BLADES...
IT'S THE GUNDAM
SEVEN SWORDS.
SO, THE EXIA IS
FINALLY LIVING UP
TO ITS DEVELOPMENT CODE.
(Grunts)
HEY, WHAT'S UP WITH HIM?
I RUSHED ALL THE WAY OUT
HERE TO THIS LITTLE ISLAND
JUST TO SHOW HIM
THE BLADES.
YOU'D THINK HE'D BE A LITTLE
MORE GRATEFUL THAN THAT!
DON'T WORRY, HE'S
PLENTY GRATEFUL OLD MAN.
WHAT?
SEE, SETSUNA
IS INFATUATED
WITH EVERYTHING
ABOUT THE EXIA.
EXIA.
MY GUNDAM.
IT'S THE OTHERS...
Newscaster:
IT IS TWELVE NOON.
ON JNN NEWS TODAY,
A SPECIAL REPORT
ON THE JOINT MILITARY
EXERCISE TAKING PLACE
IN THE MORALIAN REPUBLIC
WITH THE AEU FORCES,
CODE NAME
"OPERATION DAWN".
(Quiet murmuring)
THERE ARE OVER ONE HUNDRED
MOBILE SUITS
FROM THE TWO COMBINED FORCES
TAKING PART IN THE EXERCISE,
BUT THE REAL QUESTION IS:
WHY CONDUCT
DOES THIS INTEREST YOU?
HUH?
HI.
Bartender:
WELCOME, SIR.
AH...
AN UNE PUREE.
RIGHT AWAY SIR.
HOW DO YOU INTERPRET
MORALIA'S RECENT ACTIONS?
LET'S NOT
TALK ABOUT THAT.
WE HAVEN'T SEEN EACH
OTHER IN A WHILE.
YEAH, SINCE
GRADUATE SCHOOL, RIGHT?
HOW MANY YEARS
HAS IT BEEN?
(Laughing):
KEEP QUIET,
I DON'T WANT PEOPLE
TO FIND OUT HOW OLD I AM.
I ALREADY KNOW
HOW OLD YOU ARE.
AND HERE YOU ARE, SIR.
WHEN A WOMAN'S REAL AGE
IS MENTIONED,
SHE LOSES
SOME OF HER YOUTH.
AND DO YOU HAVE ANY DATA
TO SUPPORT THIS THEORY?
(Laughs)
YOU HAVEN'T CHANGED A
BIT, HAVE YOU, BILLY?
YOU KNOW, I'M GLAD
YOU CALLED ME UP.
OH! I FEEL GREAT!
I FEEL TIRED.
THE ANTI‐GUNDAM
TASK FORCE?
WHAT KIND OF
A NAME IS THAT?
IT WAS JUST
FORMED RECENTLY
SO IT DOESN'T REALLY
HAVE AN OFFICIAL NAME YET.
AND SO YOU'VE BEEN ASSIGNED
TO THIS TASK FORCE?
YEAH, BUT I'M
NOT ALONE.
WOULD YOU BELIEVE OUR TECHNICAL
CHIEF IS PROFESSOR RALPH EIFMAN?
THE PROFESSOR?
YEAH, HE'S BEEN INVALUABLE.
HE ALREADY FIGURED OUT
THE CONCEPT BEHIND
THE PARTICLES
EMITTED BY THE GUNDAMS.
HMM... THAT
SOUNDS INTERESTING.
WHAT KIND OF PARTICLE IS IT?
I WANT TO KNOW TOO
BUT HE WON'T TELL ME
NO MATTER HOW MANY
TIMES I ASK HIM.
IS THAT SO?
THAT'S A SHAME.
AH, NEVER MIND THAT.
SO, WHAT ARE YOU
UP TO NOW?
WELL...
A LOT OF THINGS.
LISTEN, ABOUT THAT TIME...
I'VE FORGOTTEN ABOUT IT.
I SEE.
THAT'S FINE THEN.
I'M JUST GLAD WE'VE
RECONNECTED.
YEAH.
(Gasps)
THIS IS NICE, TOO!
HOW ABOUT THIS ONE?
CUTE!
LET ME SLEEP...
Shirin:
AS WE EXPECTED, WE WERE
ONLY ABLE TO GET FOOD AID.
DON'T SAY IT LIKE IT'S
A FOREGONE CONCLUSION.
WE HAVE TO GET TECHNICAL
SUPPORT... SOMEHOW.
I'M SURE YOU'VE
SEEN THE NEWS BY NOW.
IT LOOKS LIKE MORALIA
IS HEADING STRAIGHT
FOR A CONFRONTATION
WITH CELESTIAL BEING.
IF THERE'S A CHANCE OF WAR
BREAKING OUT,
I'LL HAVE YOU RETURN HOME.
(Thinking)
AGAIN, CELESTIAL BEING...
EVEN HERE.
Al‐Saachez:
A JOINT EXERCISE?
I NEVER THOUGHT THE AEU
WOULD TAKE PART.
Commander:
THE FRUIT OF DIPLOMATIC EFFORTS.
WE CAN'T ALWAYS BE GETTING THE
SHORT END OF THE STICK.
THE AEU BETTER SHOW
UP AND DO THEIR PART.
Al Saachez:
(Chuckles)
NO KIDDING.
I WANT YOU TO USE
THIS MACHINE.
A NEW AEU MODEL?
IT WAS A DEVELOPMENT
TEST MACHINE
BUT OUR COMPANY'S ENGINEERING
BRANCH TUNED IT UP.
YOU WANT ME TO BEAT
A GUNDAM WITH THIS?
CAPTURE ONE.
(Scoffs)
EASIER SAID
THAN DONE.
WE'RE PREPARED
TO PAY YOU MORE
MONEY THAN YOU
CAN IMAGINE.
(Whistles)
NOW THAT...
IS TEMPTING INDEED.
(Brakes squeal)
I'VE BEEN WAITING FOR YOU.
HERE WE ARE.
COME ON,
I'LL SHOW YOU THE WAY.
IMPRESSIVE, WANG LIU‐MEI.
THIS IS ALL EXCELLENT.
WHY, THANK YOU
VERY MUCH.
Hong‐Long:
THIS SHOWS HOW THE MORALIAN
AND AEU FORCES ARE DEPLOYED.
Sumeragi:
AS WELL AS THE PMC TRUST...
AND IT'S IN REAL‐TIME.
WHEN DID YOU
HACK THIS?
OH, JUST BEFORE BREAKFAST.
THE MISSION WILL GET UNDERWAY AT
ZERO HUNDRED HOURS AS PLANNED.
WE'RE GOING TO TARGET EVERYTHING
THAT IS HOSTILE TO US.
ROGER THAT.
AH, YOU MET WITH
KUJO, DID YOU?
AND HOW IS SHE DOING?
JUST FINE.
DID YOU DISCUSS
THE INCIDENT?
I ASKED HER...
SHE SAID SHE'D
FORGOTTEN.
I SEE...
KUJO? ARE THEY
TALKING ABOUT
WHAT HAPPENED WITH
THAT COMBAT FORECASTER?
SIR, I'M GETTING A
VISUAL FROM THE SCENE.
IT'S ON THE MONITOR.
(Computer beeping)
WHAT'S THAT
EQUIPMENT?
THEY'RE NOT
IN OUR DATA.
CELESTIAL BEING
IS SERIOUS THIS TIME.
VISUAL CONFIRMATION OF
GUNDAMS. POINT A4576.
LOOKS LIKE THE ENEMY
MANAGED TO SPOT US.
OKAY, ALL MACHINES, RESPOND
ACCORDING TO THE MISSION PLAN.
KEEP THE CODED LINES
OPEN AT ALL TIMES.
EXPECT REVISIONS TO
THE PLAN FROM MISS SUMERAGI.
ROGER THAT.
ROGER.
MORALIA HAS JUST DECLARED
A STATE OF EMERGENCY!
URGENT REPORT!
PREPARE THE GRAPHICS!
HURRY UP WITH THE BREAKING
NEWS UPDATE GET MOVING!
RIGHT!
THEY'RE MAKING THEIR MOVE NOW!
IF THE REPUBLIC OF MORALIA HAS
DECLARED A STATE OF EMERGENCY
THEN THAT MEANS
CELESTIAL BEING
HAS BEGUN ITS ARMED
INTERVENTION AND THE FIGHTING
THEY HAVING A WAR?
IT LOOKS LIKE IT.
ANY GUNDAMS YET?
WHY DO THIS?
WHAT?
IT DOESN'T MAKE SENSE, LOUISE.
CELESTIAL BEING RESCUED US
NOW THEY'RE
STARTING A WAR THEMSELVES?
DOING THIS ISN'T GOING TO
CHANGE THE WORLD A BIT.
IT JUST CREATES HATE.
THEY'RE PLUNGING
THE WORLD INTO CHAOS.
YOU HEAR THEM, RIBBONS?
I KNOW I CAN...
ALL THE EVILS
THROUGHOUT THE WORLD.
ENEMY AIR SQUADRON
SPOTTED IN E‐332.
JUST LIKE MISS SUMERAGI'S
FORECAST SAID...
(Guns blasting)
WHAT THE...?
I CAN'T EVADE THIS!
(Boom)
ENEMY FORMATION DESTROYED.
THERE ARE NO CHANGES TO YOUR
MISSION PLAN, KYRIOS...
ROGER.
CONTINUING INTERVENTION.
DYNAMES AND VIRTUE
ARE SWITCHING
TO ARMED
INTERVENTION IN D883.
(Guns blasting)
ALRIGHT HARO, YOU TAKE
CARE OF SHIELD CONTROL!
LEAVE IT TO ME!
Laughing:
I DON'T EVEN NEED TO TAKE AIM!
AT THIS RATE...!
WATCH BEHIND YOU!
Chuckling: I'M READY FOR YOUR
SNEAK ATTACKS!
VIRTUE, PREPARING TO
ELIMINATE HELLION SQUAD.
THERE YOU ARE!
YOU'RE A DIFFERENT MODEL
FROM THE LAST TIME,
BUT YOU'RE STILL A GUNDAM,
AREN'T YOU?!
THAT MEANS YOU
ARE OBVIOUSLY MY ENEMY!
YOU HAVE ENEMY MOBILE SUITS
COMING IN FAST FROM G653.
ROGER.
I WILL ELIMINATE
THE TARGETS.
WHAT THE HECK WAS THAT...?!
READY...
RESUMING MISSION.
VIRTUE, PHASE ONE
CLEARED...
NOW PROCEEDING
TO PHASE TWO.
KYRIOS HAS DEALT WITH
ENEMY AERIAL FORCES,
MOVING ON TO PHASE TWO.
ALTER DYNAMES'
MISSION PLAN TO C5.
ROGER THAT.
THE POWER OF THE
GUNDAM MEISTERS...
WE'VE ONLY JUST BEGUN
TO SHOW OUR POWER.
WHAT IS EXIA'S STATUS?
ENGAGING ENEMY FORCES
AT T554 AS PLANNED.
♪
(Shots firing)
(Thud)
EXIA, PHASE ONE COMPLETE.
PROCEEDING TO‐‐
(Gasps)
A NEW MODEL...
(Shots blasting)
WHAT?
(Computer beeps)
HE'S READING MY MOVES!
(Laughing)
Al‐Saachez:
NICE MACHINE.
SHAME ABOUT THE PILOT, THOUGH!
WHAT DO YOU SAY,
MR. GUNDAM?
I KNOW THAT VOICE...
YOU'RE INTERFERING
WITH MY BUSINESS!
(Gasps)
NO... IT CAN'T BE!
I'VE GOT A BONUS
RIDING ON THIS!
IT IS HIM...
WELL, GUNDAM...YOU'RE MINE.
♪
Narrator:
ACTING UPON MORALS
IS PART OF BEING HUMAN,
BUT SO IS ACTING
FOR PERSONAL GAIN.
A BRIEF VICTORY AND THEN
THE DESPAIR
THAT LIES BEYOND IT...
NEXT EPISODE,
"UNREWARDED SOULS".
THE TRUE MERITS OF
THE GUNDAMS ARE QUESTIONED.