[ANN] My story is set
in the olden days,
when we of France were
still at war with England.
There was a young witch
living near our village,
who hated wars with every
beat of her fiery heart.
Her name was Maria.
The same as the Blessed Mother,
and just like her
holiest of namesakes.
Maria was a virgin.
[bells ringing]
[FARMER A, MERCENARY A grunt]
Lay down, coward!
Jamais!
If you keep coming,
we'll kill you all!
[MERCENARY C]
What did you say?
[MERCENARY D]
Die, you peasant!
[MERCENARY CAPTAIN]
By order of Count Villandrando.
I command you peasants
to lay down arms!
Surrender and you
may yet see the dawn!
The Devil can take your count!
You'll have only
more corpses from us!
Let L'ecorceur win
his gold in battle!
[ALL gasp]
[MERCENARY CAPTAIN] All of
France is our battlefield.
Even with no war to fight,
my men must eat!
[MERCENARY E]
If we had a real fight,
we'd waste no time
on your petty village.
[MERCENARY F]
Blame that witch!
She's the one stopping it!
[MERCENARY G]
Then again,
there're things
worth taking here
what you can't find
on no battlefield!
--[MERCENARY H grunts]
--[FEMALE VILLAGER B screams]
[MERCENARY I,J]
Huh?
[roars]
[MERCENARY CAPTAIN]
What? A wyvern!
[MERCENARIES gasp]
--[MERCENARY K whimpers]
--[FEMALE VILLAGER C winces]
[dog yelps]
Our father, who art in heaven,
hallowed be thy name!
[MERCENARY CAPTAIN]
Run! Fall back!
[roars]
[EZEKIEL] Hey! I can't
see what's happening!
Priapus! What are you doing?
Let go of my face!
Don't you do it!
Just hold on tight.
It'd be my pleasure.
And speaking of my pleasure,
could we do something
about my lack thereof?
We will. Keep your pants on.
There's no risk of my
taking them off right now!
Not with my dreadful lack!
Unhand me this
nstant, castrato!
--Silence! Both of you!
--[EZEKIEL] Let go of me!
I am a herald of the Lord!
[PRIAPUS]
What else am I going to grab?
[MARIA]
Later, Priapus!
What new foolishness now?
It's hard to say.
[BERNARD]
Je vois.
So, that forest is
the heart of it?
[GILBERT]
Oui.
So say the villagers all
around the monastery.
They claim to have seen
Maria flying into the fray.
She continues to
summon creatures
against French and
English soldiers alike.
They say she recently drove
Rodrigo de Villandrando's
routiers out of a village.
She never takes a
moment's respite, does she?
Not a one.
And there are rumors of
the Archangel Michael
descending upon a village
where she appeared.
Do you believe she is trying
to carve out her own realm,
Brother Bernard?
[BERNARD]
I cannot yet say.
[panting]
[EZEKIEL]
How dare you fly off without me?
Moreover, how oft must
I say that you are
forbidden from using magic
in battle and before others?
[MARIA]
Yeah.
I found this odd stick
in the village green.
Whaddaya think it could be?
Some new weapon?
[EZEKIEL] Hey! I am
still admonishing you!
I am a Messenger
of the Lord,
proxy of the Archangel Michael!
[PRIAPUS]
And it continues.
[muffled arguing]
[ARTEMIS]
I'm finally home.
[PRIAPUS]
Ah, welcome back, Artemis.
There's not one muscle in
my body that doesn't ache.
At least I can promise there'll
be no war in the east today.
What's new?
[PRIAPUS] A rout of sell-swords
attacked the village,
Maria did her magic
and chased them off.
The real problem is Ezekiel.
[EZEKIEL] Are you
even listening, Maria?
Do you think I am
blind just because
you order that runt
to cover my eyes?
She's been going at it
like that since you left.
[ARTEMIS]
Well, it's good to see
that she takes
pride in her labors.
Oh!
Priapus!
That looks simply
mouth-watering!
--Nice job, garcon!
--[PRIAPUS grunts]
[PRIAPUS]
All I can poke at, is this.
[door clatters]
I'm home, Maria.
Welcome back.
Maybe she'll listen to you,
for she's certainly not
listening to the
voice of reason!
[MARIA gasps]
[EZEKIEL gasps]
[ARTEMIS gasps]
[animals holler]
Men have remade
their favorite act
in the guise of a weapon.
--Mon Dieu.
--[EZEKIEL gasps]
What madness is this?
A weapon of such spite
could throw the whole
world into chaos.
It's already in chaos,
all because of you!
[MARIA grunts]
[EZEKIEL] I've been lenient,
but when you next defy Heaven,
Saint Michael will hear of it!
[ARTEMIS]
Ah, that reminds me.
Should she lose her magic,
what fate would befall
her innocent familiars?
I cannot say for sure.
More than likely
you would revert
to your original forms
without a witch to enchant you.
Well, that seems
rather boring, doesn't it?
I like having
this body, thank you.
[VIV]
Maria!
[ALL]
Huh?
[VIV]
Maria the witch?
Yes, and, you are?
Huh. It's about time I
made your acquaintance.
You can call me Viv, love.
Great. Another.
I think she's a witch
from across the Channel.
Is there something
I can do for you?
[VIV] I stand before you to
present a formal complaint.
I ask that you kindly stop your
interference in the warfare.
[MARIA]
What?
[VIV] The other witches
are growing frustrated.
[MARIA]
Are they, now?
You want to protect
this little kingdom
you've carved out.
We understand,
but your interruptions
are causing more
harm than good, yeah?
Really, all we're asking is that
you leave the
battles to us, agreed?
[MARIA grumbles]
[VIV] Let France and
England squabble over
who's sitting on
what throne and where,
and we witches can
make a tidy fortune.
Oh! Here's a thought!
Why don't you consider joining
our little confederation?
I can put in a few good
words on your behalf.
Everyone knows you're
something special, Maria.
It seems they're all the same,
no matter where they hail from.
And why would I want that?
[VIV]
Huh?
[MARIA] I have no
interest in money at all.
I just want to help these
people live in peace.
Honestly?
Yes, of course! This land
has suffered enough already!
It's time the fighting
came to an end.
I will not stay my hand
until the armies do.
You're serious?
Are you touched in the head?
What?
If you get your stupid peace,
how will those bloody
soldiers earn a living?
I guess they can all just learn
how to tend a farm or something!
That's an honest trade.
That's a lovely
fantasy you have,
but quite far from the truth.
You don't have to act like
your holy namesake
with me, you know?
[grunts]
If the wars suddenly end,
witches and soldiers both
will lose their livelihood.
Villandrando's mercenaries
only started looting
because there were no
real battles to fight.
Your code of honor is
just an excuse to shove
your own cock-eyed
beliefs onto everybody else!
Besides, if you and yours
keep barging into these fights,
Heaven is gonna come
down hard on you!
[gasps]
That's the truth.
Saint Michael already told her
what would happen if
she lost her virginity.
Hold on here.
[laughing]
You mean to tell me that
you're actually still a maid?
Truly? I simply
cannot believe it!
Don't you have
somewhere else to be?
In any case, this works
out rather well for us.
Time we were rid of
that pesky virginity.
What? Like, now?
It's brilliant!
Oh, you're in for a
hell of a time, Maria!
But I, this is, I mean,
this is all so out of the blue.
Don't worry about a thing!
I swear! There's no joy
sweeter in this life
than taking a
man to your bed.
Hey! Too close! Too tight!
Claiming a man who
fits you perfectly
has its own kind of magic.
Surely you would agree.
[ARTEMIS]
It's magical, I can't deny it.
And what say you,
who hails from Heaven above?
[gasps]
Truly there's no
pleasure on earth
greater than such
carnal abandon.
I refuse to answer.
'Tis unseemly of one such as I.
[MARIA]
Wha--?
Ezekiel!
I trusted you!
Even you know about--?
I wasn't blushing
because I know!
It's a filthy, unclean subject
and I'll have no part of it,
you hear me?
Right. Easy.
[VIV]
You know what?
You virgins are
such a boring lot.
Once they're finally abed,
they do naught
but shiver in fear,
mewling like a lost kitten.
As though they're ashamed
of having a little
fun now and again.
Is it true the first
time hurts a lot?
Sure, at first. So much you
fear you'll split in two.
But, if he sees to his duty...
[VIV] Like to know a
bit more, would you?
A-A little.
My mistress is
curious today.
Good! Then it's sorted.
I shall scare you up a lover!
[MARIA]
Huh? Y-You don't mean!
[VIV] You still want
to lose it, right?
Well, yeah, but...
I'll need to prepare.
So much to do, so little time.
It's all rather
complicated, you see.
Have it your way.
Then for today, let's have
you watch me at it.
I'll explain how everything
works as we go along.
Yeah?
[MARIA]
Yeah. Great.
Food's ready, everyone.
[VIV]
Uh?
[PRIAPUS gasps]
[VIV]
Ah! He's so cute! Is he yours?
He's my incubus, but he
hasn't quite, y'know.
Another virgin?
My lucky day. Come on!
[PRIAPUS]
Uh! Wait! Wait! I, um!
[MARIA gasps]
[VIV] Come, come, Maria,
we mustn't delay our work!
The fun part's coming up!
[PRIAPUS]
You don't understand!
Not there!
You're not going to--!
[PRIAPUS screams]
What kind of evil
witch are you?
Are you insane?
You left off the best part!
To be fair, I tried to warn you.
[PRIAPUS screams]
[VIV]
Heed me, virgin!
When I come back,
that boy best be complete.
And I mean really complete!
Wait a second. What do
you mean "come back"?
[VIV]
A three-legged stool!
Dirty. Oh so dirty!
Unclean, unclean, unclean,
--unclean, unclean.
--[PRIAPUS grunts]
[hog squeels]
[DRUNKARD laughs]
Those English bastards.
Thank ya, lad.
De rien.
[GALFA] Maria's causing
plenty of problems.
That girl don't know when to
leave well enough alone, right?
Huh.
[GALFA] If that witch won't
let us have a proper fight,
I think we'd best move on.
Looks like The captain's
over there haggling
with the noble for our payment.
So, we're marooned
in this backwater.
It's not so bad.
You'll have all your coin
back soon as I'm paid.
[JOSEPH]
No need. It's yours.
Huh?
[JOSEPH] If I need something,
I'll ask my Lord.
He's a generous man,
and glad to help.
I hope that coin can
help your comrades.
[scoffs]
Joseph,
you aren't cut out for
a soldier's lot in life.
Truly?
But, if you are just
givin' gold away,
I'll gladly take my share.
And on the topic of
takin' one's share.
You're still a virgin, aintcha.
[JOSEPH sputters]
Well! We can have
that cured in a trice.
We've a doxy at the camp
who will scratch
your itch right quick.
[JOSEPH]
Uh. You don't have to.
Why not? Think you're
too good for that type?
I meant no disrespect.
Uh, how do I put this?
There's this lady.
[GALFA] I get it,
yer lookin' to get unlaced
by that other girl, aren't ya?
No, but Mari--!
No. It would be
dishonorable to think of a lady
in such a position. You know?
[GALFA]
Hmm.
I'm just a sell-sword.
That's what you think!
What I think, is maybe
you drank too much.
Shut up! Get offa me!
I don't need you to hold me up.
'Course not.
I'll pay it all back.
Every single coin.
I'm not talking
alms from you, boy!
Please, Galfa. I swear
that's not what I--!
[GALFA]
They're all I got to my name.
That's all gonna change,
you hear me?
Just you wait, Joseph.
I've got a dream, damn it all!
I'm plantin' my sword in the
chest of every one
of my enemies,
and I'm climbin' that stinkin'
pile of corpses to the very top!
I'll get knighted!
Or made a noble!
They'll bow to me!
I'm gonna be king, you hear me?
An' to get that
crown on my head,
there ain't nothing I won't do!
I'll do anything!
--[GALFA grunts]
--[JOSEPH gasps]
[JOSEPH]
Galfa!
Please just tell me I'm right.
Ain't it about time that
some luck came my way?
Yes. Come on.
Let's get you to bed.
A king has got to have
his rest, after all.
Well then.
Time for my first decree.
[JOSEPH]
Huh?
A boy does what he's told,
but it's a man decides.
[JOSEPH] All I know is...
I want to be more.
Your code of honor,
is an excuse to shove your
beliefs onto everybody else!
[MARIA]
Peace... War.
Ah, why?! It shouldn't
be like this!
What's wrong with simple peace!
Hey, Priapus!
[PRIAPUS]
Hm?
[MARIA] Bring this medicine
to Martha, understand?
As you wish.
Ezekiel, you should go with him.
[EZEKIEL]
What?
[MARIA]
Yeah.
Do the shopping
while you're out.
Do not seek to command
me like a servant!
[grunts, yells]
And grab us some fresh
eggs if you see any!
[PRIAPUS]
Got it!
[EZEKIEL] Why do I have
to go on the shopping trip?
[PRIAPUS] You're eating
at our table, aren't you?
I am a herald of the Lord
and you are a cook.
Can't you do this on
your own, Priapus?
[PRIAPUS] Maria needs some
alone time to think things over.
[EZEKIEL]
What things?
New ways in which to bedevil me?
[PRIAPUS grunts]
[EZEKIEL] Hey, isn't that
a village down there?
Let's stop and do
the stupid shopping.
[PRIAPUS]
Ezekiel, wait!
You won't find anything to buy.
It's empty.
Sickness ravaged the place.
The Black Plague.
[EZEKIEL] So, she's not
protecting everyone after all.
[PRIAPUS]
Huh?
[EZEKIEL] Maria's not the saint
she paints herself out to be.
She only helps those who
come begging at her door.
This is the proof.
She could have easily saved
the people of this village.
Instead, it's a charnel house.
[PRIAPUS]
That's enough!
[EZEKIEL yells]
Wait! Your claws!
They're very sharp!
Very painful! Ah!
Ow, ow, ow, ow!
[EZEKIEL yelps, grunts]
You're the slowest
winged creature
that I have ever seen. And you
simply cannot stay silent.
I demand to know why!
What right has she to decide
which village may perish?
Well, your God didn't
save them either. Right?
Everything goes
according to His plan.
It's not for us to question
the will of the Most High.
[sighs] Must be easy for you.
All that's required is
that you have some faith.
Oh really?
So you think it's easy
having to explain myself
to the likes of a
half-made familiar?
[growls]
[ANN]
Bonjour, vous duex!
[BOTH gasp]
I bet Maria sent you here
with the medicine for
Grandmother, huh?
Thank you, Priapus and Dovey!
My name is Ezekiel!
[bells ringing]
Ah, Maria.
It sounds as though she's
back to her usual self.
[PRIAPUS] She's full of the
same strong spirit as before.
Flitting hither and
yon through the skies.
Had I the strength to go,
I'd gladly pay her a visit.
Alas, these bones aren't as
young as they used to be.
When I was a
younger woman,
I would play with
Maria every day.
[MARIA giggles]
[MARTHA] We spent each
season in its turn together.
I cherish every memory.
[PRIAPUS]
Maria often smiles
at the thought of
you as well, madame.
Her medicine has granted
me more days than
I could have seen otherwise.
I am forever in her debt.
I thank her every visit!
Don't worry!
That's a good girl, dearie.
May the Lord bless
and keep our Maria.
Heresy.
--[ANN] Huh?
--[PRIAPUS] Hm?
[EZEKIEL]
You seem devout, at first blush.
A servant of God Almighty.
But, you pray for
a witch's safety.
You of all should
know full well,
that her magic defies
the will of Heaven.
But she's nice.
[EZEKIEL] Receiving
ministrations by her hand!
You should be
ashamed of yourself!
Hey!
[EZEKIEL] To pray for her
is mockery of the faith!
Long before dear
Ann here was born,
the towns and villages of
France were hit with pestilence.
[EZEKIEL huffs]
Would that I could
forget those dark days.
All around us,
people perished by the hundreds.
The nearby village
was ravaged by it.
We were certain ours was next.
We prayed night and day for
God above to deliver us.
His Mercy came in
the form of Maria.
She gave us medicine
of her own devising.
Medicine that spared every
one of us from the black death.
Had we died, my precious
Ann never would have been born.
How can I not be
grateful to Maria, then?
But, still.
I worship God in heaven
as devoutly as anybody,
but He works in mysterious ways,
and I believe that
she is one of them.
[MARIA yelps]
[MARIA grunts]
I heard that one
of your children
drank water from a tainted well.
If you give them this, I swear
their sickness will end.
In the name of Almighty God,
I command you to leave us!
[MARIA gasps]
[VILLAGER murmur]
[FRENCH PRIEST] No child of God
shall live by a witch's grace!
[gasps]
[FRENCH PRIEST]
Get thee hence, hell-spawn!
We are safe in
the light of Christ!
Thanks again! Travel safe!
[EZEKIEL] Those that ask,
she will save, but not others.
Are you still not satisfied?
[EZEKIEL]
Wait, Priapus.
[EZEKIEL] If everyone wished it,
would Maria, become like God?
[PRIAPUS]
Huh?
[EZEKIEL] Why're you
looking at me like that?
[PRIAPUS] You did
say "become like God".
Ah! Well, I certainly
didn't mean become like the God!
Why to even speak such a
thing aloud is a cardinal sin!
All I'm saying is that I
want to understand why
she does the things she does.
[EZEKIEL] And it seems these
people really respect her.
If you still don't get it,
there is one way.
Just ask her yourself.
Huh?
[PRIAPUS] That's the best
way to an answer, right?
You have plenty
of opportunities.
We gotta finish shopping.
Come on.
[EZEKIEL]
Um.
[PRIAPUS]
Yeah?
[EZEKIEL] Please don't,
carry me in your claws again.
Well then, you had
better keep up, right?
I'll fly slow for you.
I think she wanted
fresh eggs, isn't that right?
Lead on, Sir Cook.
"Sir Cook," huh?
I wish Maria'd let me
barter my ladle for a lance.
[OLD VILLAGER grunting]
Our Father, who art in heaven,
hallowed be thy name.
[GILBERT] The final soul
in the northern village
has been called to his reward.
[BERNARD] The hamlet that
suffered most under the plague?
[GILBERT]
Yes, Brother.
He was the only one
to survive its wrath.
[GILBERT]
He lived a devout life,
offering daily prayers for
the repose of the dead.
[BERNARD]
He was blessed.
Truly the definition
of faith in practice.
His work must be honored.
It is the very least
the we can do for him.
And still, not nearly enough.
Yes.
We've news of the witch's
movements as well.
It seems that the
surrounding forest
is connected to Maria
in some strange way.
What would you
have us do, Brother?
It would be easy
to disregard this
and keep silent, yet...
Gilbert.
Carry a missive
to our noble lord.
[GILBERT]
Yes. Of course.
[BERNARD]
Say that Brother Bernard
has urgent news to convey.
News of battle which
have yet to begin.
I did what I could.
Now it's on Galfa.
[JEAN]
Heh! What a wretched opponent!
[MARIA]
It's such a conundrum.
One that I'll have
to figure out someday.
He'll kill him!
Begin!