[ARTEMIS] Are you sure
you're well enough to travel?
[PRIAPUS]
Artemis is right.
Viv did say you were
welcome to rest there
for a few more days,
if it please you.
True, but it's Edwina's
house, n'est pas?
[EZEKIEL] Let us be clear
about one thing!
You cannot use your magic with
such wild abandon any longer!
[PRIAPUS]
Nobody is going to hurt her.
That includes you, y'know!
[EZEKIEL] If she hadn't
flouted the will of Heaven
this whole time,
it wouldn't be an issue!
[PRIAPUS]
It only became one
when you went tattling
to your master!
[MARIA]
Hey! Both of you!
That's quite enough of that.
Huh?
[FEMALE CLANS FOLK]
A skirmish broke out
and the child took a
stray arrow to her hand.
So we came to have
a witch tend it.
You came so far for a poultice.
I thought that your clan
hailed from the north?
[FEMALE CLANS FOLK]
'Tis true.
[MARIA]
What of those witches?
The Duke of Buckingham's
cavalry charged through,
making a ruin of our
lands and our homes.
The witches scattered
in the chaos.
Okay. That should do it.
You were very brave.
[CLANS FOLK CHILD A giggles]
Within the last month,
we heard of Falaise and
Rouen fortifying their walls.
The fighting is not
like to abate anon.
They're nothing
if not persistent.
These humans are willing
to wage war forever.
I think these woodlands will
remain peaceful for a time yet.
Why not stay, and
take your rest here?
[MALE CLANS FOLK 8 grunts]
The offer is a kind one.
Would that we could stay,
but we must journey back again.
[MALE CLANS FOLK A]
Humans often forget about us,
and our powers do
wane as of late,
but battered or not,
that land is still our home.
Yes. I suppose so.
The wound will close
up in a day or so.
[CLANS FOLK CHILD]
Thanks a lot, Maria!
[MALE CLANS FOLK A]
Well, 'tis time to journey on.
Good luck to you!
No matter who fights who
over what foolish
title or bit of land,
it is still the weak who suffer
the most for their warring.
What do you mean?
[MARIA] The innocents
caught in these battles
are always told the same thing.
"God is grieving for your loss."
As though this madness
is all their fault.
What sort of hypocrisy is that?
Well, it clearly wasn't
us who taught them that!
[MARIA]
That may be so, but still.
Ah, forgot to tell you.
A young girl came by
while you were away.
Huh?
[ANN]
Maria! Maria! Please!
I need more medicine!
Grandmother's sick!
[ARTEMIS] I fear something
has happened to Martha.
Priapus! Go the village
and check on her!
[PRIAPUS]
Right!
[GUILLAUME]
So, the witch was wounded,
but still she draws
breath, you say?
[JOSEPH]
Yes.
My lord, she needs time to
rest and recover her vigor.
It would not be prudent to
rely on her interventions.
Ah, no loss.
Boy!
Yes.
Deliver this to
Galfa without delay.
Uh! Galfa, my lord?
[GUILLAUME]
Aye. Your worldly friend.
If he wants to command
the Red Arm Brothers,
he shall have need of it.
[FEMALE VILLAGERS chatter]
[DENIS] We owe you more
than we could e'er repay,
Reverend Brother.
Even yesterday she could
barely lift her head.
[GILBERT]
Not at all.
'Twas God Above through
Brother Bernard's medicine
that healed her.
[GILBERT]
Rejoice, good sir.
It is fortunate that
your mother remains
a devoted servant
of the Lord God.
Being of his flock,
Brother Bernard himself greatly
desires to attend upon her.
Huh? Ah, yes!
Yes, of course!
[ANN sighs]
[PRIAPUS]
Ann. Ann.
[ANN]
Uh?
Shhh.
[PRIAPUS] Good. It sounds
like Martha's on the mend.
[ANN]
Yeah.
The monk brought Grandmother
special medicine
so she could breathe again.
But then...
What's wrong?
Well, the monk...
He and Papa were
talking about things.
And he found out about
Maria's medicine.
And he said that
Maria's medicine
was what made her so
sick in the first place.
[gasps]
[ANN] He said an evil witch was
poisoning her the whole time.
He said that?
Tell me the truth!
Maria wouldn't
do that, would she?
[PRIAPUS]
Of course not!
[ANN] So, the monk was
lying to him, is that it?
Yes, he was!
Why? Why would he
lie about Maria?
[PRIAPUS gasps]
I don't know.
[MERCENARIES, VILLAGERS chatter]
It's quiet n'est pas?
Beg pardon, but is Galfa about?
Huh? Oh, the Captain.
[JOSEPH]
Captain?
There. In the
well-appointed tent.
Many thanks, good sir.
[MERCENARY B]
Hey! You there?
What is it? I'm already
beset with errands.
The quartermaster--
[MERCENARY B]
You're just gonna kneel down
and lick the boots of
that scum Galfa now, huh?
[MERCENARY A]
Please! I'm sorry!
Let me up!
I meant no offense!
[MERCENARY B grunts]
Eyes on my face, Joseph.
Forgive me
Let the kid look at it.
Your arm is quite
a fearsome sight.
Shut your mouth!
Ah, could be worse.
I mean, one less arm beats
hell outta one less head.
[JOSEPH]
I bring a gift.
[GALFA]
Huh?
[JOSEPH]
From milord, Le Comte.
[GALFA] Stay a moment.
I've a question needs answering.
What is it?
[GALFA] Why did that witch
appear on the battlefield again?
[gasps]
[GALFA]
Joseph.
It was on you to talk
her outta doing that.
I-I'm so sorry.
[GALFA]
So what happened?
She use her magic
on you or something?
No. Nothing like that at all.
I swear on my oath.
Lady Maria was only seeking
to end the fighting
as best she knew how.
[GALFA] Heh, heh. And all
that for the small cost
of losing a battle
we were bound to win.
Leaving behind my shield arm
and the bastards killing Yvain.
[gasps]
[GALFA]
And now, I'm stuck here.
Captaining the Brothers in
a war raging twice as strong.
[LOLOTTE]
Hmph.
[JOSEPH]
Truly. I am sorry.
[GALFA] That's rich. Coming from
the boy without a scratch.
I know.
[GALFA] Heh. Tell me,
where is the witch now?
Priapus should have
been back by now!
Back? What about his front?
[MARIA growls]
Try not to worry.
He'd return at once if Martha
had great need of you.
Well maybe, but it would
be better to know--!
[grunts]
Damn if the Britons
haven't rallied
in the wake of our ambush.
More blood will be spilt.
[gasps]
[GALFA] You see, rumors
fly about my camp, boy.
Rumors?
[GALFA] Everywhere I turn, each
whisper is of Maria the witch.
The cause of our defeat.
[JOSEPH]
But, Galfa!
[GALFA] What? You gonna
convince 'em she ain't?
Go tell the witch
to keep to her wood.
If she's smart, she'll lay low
till this anger burns down.
[LOLOTTE]
Aw, look at you.
Taking that poor little
chick under your wing.
Under my wing?
You think I... like him?
Yeah.
[GALFA]
Why d'ya say that?
Don't you gimme that look!
[GALFA]
Heh.
[LOLOTTE] No matter, then.
Just keep the troupe in coin.
Captain Galfa.
Filthy lucre makes
the world go 'round.
[GALFA scoffs]
Stop acting like my wife.
[PRIAPUS]
Joseph!
[JOSEPH gasps]
[PRIAPUS] Thank goodness.
I've been looking for you.
Please, come! We need
you at Maria's right away!
What?
You need to help
us keep her calm.
I hurry homeward with news
she won't want to hear.
Ah. Then I know well
your trepidation.
Truly, Joseph?
Yes. I was on my
way out to see her.
[labored breathing]
They think what?!
How dare they accuse me
of such villainy?
For years I've cared for
Martha and that village!
[PRIAPUS]
I-I know, but--
[MARIA]
Me, poison Martha?
The words curdle upon my tongue!
Master. Patience! Please!
Those herbs they malign
have been keeping her alive!
Oh, damn those liars!
They're lucky
I'm such a pacifist,
or there would be hell to pay!
Maria stop!
I share in your pain.
[MARIA]
Huh?
[JOSEPH]
But you must be at ease.
But they're lying!
I would never poison--!
We know, and I'm sure
that Ann does, too.
However, what that monk
said is frightening her.
[MARIA grunts]
Understood.
Where are you going?
To the village.
Really?
By now, I'm sure the village
wants nothing to do
with the heretic Maria.
You barging in will only make
things worse for Martha.
[MARIA]
Make them worse? How?
[JOSEPH]
Unfortunately, Artemis is right.
And it's not only that village.
Misunderstanding is
quick to take wing.
[MARIA gasps]
[JOSEPH] While I don't
believe they would harm you,
it may be best if
you stayed silent.
Just for a time.
[MARIA]
Tell me why?
Why do they all just
assume the worst?
All I've ever wanted was--!
I'll tell you what
they would say!
In their eyes
you are a heretic.
Heretic?
I halt their wars,
and heal their afflicted.
And for that, I get only hate?
That's crazy!
All that you give them
are the things that
no mortal should be
able to grant another.
Some of them do think this.
You have been denied before.
[MARIA gasps]
Hey!
So you know,
about that village.
Um, well I--
No matter how you
may wish for it,
the truth cannot be changed.
You are naught but
a heretic to them.
[MARIA sighs]
The people there
don't understand you.
They will always throw stones.
They're scared. The Church
keeps them that way.
That's why...
[MARIA gasps]
[EZEKIEL]
That's why...
time after time they
will turn against you!
They've been raised to fear you!
It doesn't matter
what you do for them!
You're no better!
You know what Heaven
demands of you!
We could all be
on the same side!
But you're so stubborn!
I don't want you
to end up alone!
I can't help it!
It's who I am.
[EZEKIEL sobs]
[JOSEPH]
I must return to Le Comte.
[MARIA]
Right.
Milady.
I've seen the good
you do firsthand.
Far more than the
Church has seen.
I know what you do is right.
Even if the world
condemns you,
I have never
doubted you, milady,
and I never will.
[gasps]
Trust in the path you've chosen,
never stray from it.
Though foes may dog your steps.
I am here.
I will always be.
[gasps]
[JOSEPH]
I will never abandon you.
'Til next time.
Thank you.
I, uh...
L-Lady Maria?
[gasps]
[MERCENARY B growls]
Galfa, I know you slew Yvain!
[LOLOTTE]
Did you really, Galfa?
Guess he didn't do it.
[MERCENARY B]
Tch. I thought as much.
Look like I'll be feedin' two
traitors to my zweihander!
You got greedy.
And I see you for
exactly what you are.
A serpent.
That so?
Trouble with serpents is
they can't hold onto anything.
Kind of like you.
If there's one thing I cannot
abide, it's a Judas at the helm!
[LOLOTTE] Aahh!
Have you lost your mind?
You'd kill you own captain?
[MERCENARY B]
Why the hell not?
It's no worse than
what he did to Yvain!
You'd cut me down just to lord
over a bunch of sell-swords?
If you think you're
man enough for it,
come over here and put that
sword through my heart.
Lolotte. Open it.
[LOLOTTE grunts]
Fool woman.
You'll never ready
a firearm in time.
[gasps]
What the--?
Galfa, what the
devil is that thing?
Now, you can go
crawling back to camp,
or I can leave your bloodied
corpse out here for the animals.
[MERCENARY B chuckles]
I could never serve you!
[GALFA]
Thought so.
Fine, I'll climb over you, too.
[ARTEMIS] I put Ezekiel to
bed when she stopped crying.
[MARIA]
Thanks. Where's Priapus?
I think he left to check
the rumors in town.
[MARIA]
Ah.
So, tell me, are you
still a maid?
What?! Who just says that?
Well, you took your sweet
time bidding him adieu.
I thought you had
your way with him.
We did no such thing!
No, I guess not.
If you'd done the deed,
you'd be standing differently
right now, Master.
You're a bad owl!
[ARTEMIS laughs]
It's odd, huh?
For a long time
this place was quiet,
with only the two
of us living here.
And now there's some sort of
excitement almost every day.
You know?
Yeah, you're right.
[ARTEMIS] Listen.
Ezekiel, Joseph, Priapus, me.
We all want the best for you.
You just stay at home and put
your focus into getting better.
I'll go out, and do what I do.
[MARIA chuckles]
[ARTEMIS]
And while I'm at it,
I'll painfully do what I do
to those who speak ill of you.
Artemis!
[ARTEMIS]
Huh? This smoke!
[MARIA]
What do you want, Cernunnos?
Wait. You know it?
[CERNUNNOS]
Witch Maria, you bore witness
to the northern clan.
I did. You know them?
[CERNUNNOS]
In time long past.
They are but shadows
of their ancestors.
Faded in their weakness.
Well, you look a
bit faded yourself.
[CERNUNNOS] Your familiar
speaks the truth.
Goodness. Aren't we honest?
[CERNUNNOS]
A hollow existence is the fate
that befalls all of our kind.
It doth rest upon me.
Doth rest upon that northern
clan and thee, witch.
Speak for yourself!
[CERNUNNOS]
The fateful hour is nigh.
[MARIA gasps]
[CERNUNNOS] The people
will carve your kindnesses
out of their memories and
turn their backs upon thee.
They will forget
all that we were
with surprising ease, sorceress.
And they more the fools for it.
But...
Why even come here?
Away with you, beast!
[CERNUNNOS] Witch Maria,
why rush to their aid?
Why intervene in humankind's
futile struggles?
[MARIA gasps]
[CERNUNNOS] Become one
with us, swear unto us--
Get you gone!
[LOLOTTE grunts]
Come now. Off with ya!
That's a lovely toy, Galfa!
[GALFA]
Heh. Indeed.
I can certainly get up to
some trouble with this.
Ah. So this is the place.
[GILBERT]
Yes.
They say that the
Archangel Michael
descended upon this very spot.
If only we could
have borne witness.
Blessed be mine eyes.
Yes. Would that we had.
The honored Brother Bernard
has at last come among us.
You do us a great honor, sirrah.
[BERNARD]
I am but a humble servant.
It is at the name of Jesus
that every knee shall bend
[VALKYRIE A]
See how the Church of the World
gluts itself upon empty words.
Martha, can you hear me?
[MARTHA]
Yes.
I feel I am growing better
with each passing hour.
[BERNARD]
These are glad tidings.
Thanks to your medicine, Brother
Bernard, I am still alive.
Martha, I can take no credit.
It was the will of God.
[ANN whimpers]
Know you this.
I've never seen anyone
regain their strength
with speed such as this.
Your recovery may indeed
count as a miracle.
[BONNE, DENIS gasp]
Could it be so?
The Lord Above has granted
me more time in this life?
[BERNARD]
I am told all is not well.
You have been treated
with false medicines
at the hands of a witch.
[ANN gasps]
[MARTHA gasps]
But, she...
[BERNARD] Witches are
the most cunning of liars.
They worm their way
into your heart,
but their promises
are naught but dust.
Will you sever ties to her,
this creature of inequity?
Will you renounce her in
word and in deed evermore?
[MARTHA gasps]
Evermore?
[ANN gasps]
To tender with a witch is
unbefitting the children of God.
[MARTHA sighs]
[BERNARD]
Even now. God is merciful.
Martha, will you confess
your sin before the Almighty?
For the sake of your family.
[MARTHA]
I shall confess.
[BERNARD]
Begin.
God above, I confess
my sins to thee.
I have sinned against you
and your church on Earth.
I have fraternized with a witch.
Was it the witch
Maria, my child?
I pledge to thee.
The Witch Maria shall
never have my heart.
This I pray.
[ANN]
Grandmother?
[BERNARD]
Ego te absolvo.
Your sins have been forgiven.
Amen.
[bells ringing]
[BERNARD]
Mark me!
The insidious presence
of the witch named Maria
sows naught but
confusion and death.
Perhaps you wonder why
she would treat us ill.
She is a witch and sworn to
deliver chaos in her wake.
In her words, she brings
peace to our war-torn homeland.
But by quelling war,
she lengthens it,
and makes herself indispensible.
She profits by the discord
she claims to loathe.
The witch is clever, you see.
She clings to our dream
of peace, like a leech.
We shall achieve it with the
unyielding strength of our faith
and labor drawn out
of our own hands.
We need no witches to aid us.
They must be forgotten.
All witches must
fade from our memory.
Put your trust in
God's Holy Church.
Let the witches,
who stand opposed to order and
light never again see the sun.
Children our Brother Gilbert
here, blessed be he,
has been named a magistrate
of the Inquisition.
[gasps]
[BERNARD] May the power of his
pure faith return this village,
and its people, to the glory
of our Holy Father.
Let all of us walk in
the light of Christ our Lord.
Amen.
[BERNARD]
Bonne chance to you, Gilbert.
[GILBERT]
Ah, but Brother.
I do not deserve this,
flawed as I am.
Purity of purpose
has brought you here.
Trust in it.
I shall do all I can.
Once her purity is lost,
so too, then, is her magic.
You told me yourself, Galfa.
It matters not the
how or the wherefore.
With her virginity sundered,
she can harry us no longer.
Are you really telling
me to do this?
[BERNARD] It would make
a fitting revenge.
For all that she's
taken from you.
Brother, you're the Devil.
[BERNARD] The Devil
resideth in each of us.
Only the Lord can
keep him at bay.
I have prepared
a special incense.
I'll leave the
particulars to you.
Of course. I am not
versed in such things.
[MARIA]
When did it start?
How did I become so dedicated
to stopping battle?
[MARIA]
What am I trying to achieve?
[BERNARD] Is irrationality
the reason we need faith?
But Aristotle said
affirmation and negation
cannot both be true at once.
Ergo. Ergo. No, wait!
Is consideration of the
unchanging as a premise
wrong from the onset?