Shining blades held fast in
the hands of silent legions,
dance upon the broken
wings of Bladud!
[VIV]
Damn you, Michael!
Bloody hell!
Stay your hand.
This fight is not thine, witch.
[EZEKIEL]
Please, Viv!
[VIV]
What?! Ezekiel!
[EZEKIEL] You cannot hope to lay
hands upon a blessed Archangel!
Surrender, Viv! You must!
Not a chance in hell!
[EZEKIEL gasps]
Ever-loyal Cordelia,
I call to thee.
Show this witch
thy enduring faith!
Why are you still fighting?
For Maria!
I know you won't stand for her
to be held captive, either!
[EZEKIEL]
No, but...
[VIV] Humans ache for divine
love, but God never answers.
Do you know why?
[EZEKIEL]
Huh?
[VIV]
It's simple, really.
Almighty God knows
nothing of love.
Does he? Tell her
the truth, Michael!
Or I'll tell it for you! We
mortals are the creators of it!
You can't even comprehend
love, angel!
How could we ever be subservient
to the likes of you!
[laughs]
I'm right, aren't I?
And that's God's truth!
[gasps]
[ARTEMIS]
Viv!
Uh...
[VIV gasping]
Viv! Are you all right?
I sealed up the wound.
Nothing to it.
[ARTEMIS]
Viv!
[EZEKIEL]
Saint Michael, why?
Surely you see that was
an extreme punishment
not fitting her offense!
The girl did not earn her
punishment by raising a hand
in violence to me.
Her rebuke was meant
for the Lord of Hosts,
which cannot be countenanced.
You think her words empty?
Attend. Does wheat chastise
the farmer saying,
"'Tis not yet time
for the harvest"?
Even if such words were given,
would the farmer ever heed
the council of simple wheat?
[EZEKIEL whimpers]
Oh, I really hope Maria's
wounds have fully healed by now.
Stewed mole should suffice if
they return in need, correct?
What if the mole
isn't to her liking?
--Truly? Viv, neither?
--[knocking]
[ARTEMIS]
Edwina! Edwina, open up!
It's Viv. Please, hurry!
[EDWINA] The mole couldn't
have been that bad, surely!
[GILBERT]
Maria of the forest.
You are hereby accused
of sowing chaos
and discord while professing
yourself a heathen witch
in defiance of
the Lord, our God.
Will you confess your sin?
Since the moment of my birth,
I have been a witch.
Admitting it now will make
not a shred of difference.
[GILBERT] Have you received
the sacrament of baptism?
[MARIA]
I don't know.
I will ask this of you again.
Have you received
the sacrament--
I said I don't know!
[GUILLAUME] This is our chance,
my boy. I'll not let it pass.
What about Lady Maria?
Can you speak of nothing
else but your "Lady Maria"?
I speak of the Britons, Joseph!
[JOSEPH]
Of course, sir.
[GUILLAUME]
Those cowardly English dogs
had their very
armaments torn fresh
from their hands by some
power far greater than we are.
From their fingers, to the sky!
Mayhap some witch or spirit
drew them on, milord.
[GUILLAUME]
It matters little.
Providence stands
firm at our side.
The Britons have fled to the
walls of a nearby castle town,
with no arms to speak of.
[JOSEPH] Surely they'll loot
the town for new steel.
[GUILLAUME] What paltry arms
could mere peasants have?
Besides, 'tis but a whisper
before the thunder our cannons
can bring to bear upon them.
We will grind them to dust.
If fate should dote on us,
this could turn the entire
war to our favor.
Always more warfare.
The inquisition has only
just begun its trial,
and there is sure to be no
decision for some time.
Serve me with valor
in the coming battle,
and I'll see that
your Maria is freed.
Until then, my boy,
you must fight.
For my Lady Maria...
I will serve.
[GILBERT]
Have you no fear
of God's wrath and eternal
condemnation, witch?
You do not heed the Gospel.
You use wicked conjurations
to blunder into wars.
Do you not see your
own arrogance?
You just love the sound
of your own voice,
don't you, Inquisitor?
It is not about arrogance.
I simply despise death.
Nothing else to it.
[MERCENARIES chatter]
[MERCENARY A]
Huh?
[JOSEPH grunts]
Nice throw. You're almost cute
when you're angry, dear boy.
Enough! I demand you tell me
where that craven
Galfa ran off to!
[LOLOTTE] No idea. Maybe he's
found a new doxy to play with.
Why not try the battlefield?
That's home to Galfa.
Far more than this place is.
It's e'er the same reply!
[gasps]
Wherever I turn, fate drags
me onwards! Always to battle!
Battle! Battle! Dammit!
Even the word itself
seems to hound my heels.
Only for you, Lady Maria.
Will you confess your
sins to God Almighty?
Will you beg forgiveness for
your many lies and falsehoods?
Never! Spew your lies.
They cannot change
who I am inside.
[GILBERT] Even now, after I
have offered her confession,
and the absolution of her sins,
she remains strong
in her defiance.
She says that she will ever
remain a witch in her heart.
Our duty in this is clear.
[GILBERT]
Frere Bernard!
[BERNARD]
Yes?
[GILBERT]
What say you, Brother?
[BERNARD] Right. Yes. Gilbert.
Proceed as you see fit.
Have you lost interest
in the witch's trial?
Interest? Funny. Now there's
a word. I have faith
that you will do what you must
to put an end this matter.
[GILBERT exhales]
[EDWINA]
It was a very close thing,
but Viv will keep her life.
Although she is no less a fool
for challenging Saint Michael.
Even the Valkyries dare not face
him. What madness ensnares me?
Edwina. Maria is still held
captive, but you can help.
[EDWINA gasps]
Why ask this of me?
Are you not her friend?
I, her friend? Certainly you
jest. I hardly even know her.
[ARTEMIS]
Maria would beg to disagree.
[gasps] S-Still, even
if we truly are friends,
my powers pale in comparison
to hers and Viv's.
I could not stand
against Michael.
All I want is to work on
my mixtures in peace.
You would just abandon her?
[EDWINA gasps]
[MARTHA]
Forgive me.
I betrayed my truest friend
at the whim of the church.
But Dovey. Maria always
tried to keep us safe.
Why does the Church
want to hurt her?
[EZEKIEL] That is only, the will
of mankind's Church on Earth.
The Heavenly Host would
never harm its flock.
[ANN]
But, everyone tells me
the Church is supposed to
talk for Heaven, isn't it?
I don't understand, but...
This is all so wrong, Dovey!
Please! Tell me how I
can make it all better!
[EZEKIEL]
I wish I could tell you.
I thought seeing Martha
would help show me
the path I should take.
[JOSEPH] I will fight for
Lady Maria if I must.
When I return, we will free
her from the Inquisition.
Do we really have the time to
hesitate now? Let's go at once!
I'd like nothing more than
to storm her prison.
That said, if we should fail,
it only serves to
make things worse.
[PRIAPUS]
I'm just a familiar.
[JOSEPH gasps]
[PRIAPUS] But I know Maria
hopes more than anything
that you'll come rushing
to her rescue.
[JOSEPH] This battle
will not be my end.
I shall save Lady Maria,
and then...
And then...
[FRENCH CAPTAIN A]
Forward!
Saint Barbara,
protect this realm!
[FRENCH SOLDIERS] Saint Barbara,
Saint Barbara,
protect this realm!
[FRENCH CAPTAIN A]
Saint Barbara!
We beseech your blessing
upon these cannons!
[FRENCH SOLDIERS] Saint Barbra,
we beseech your blessing!
Saint Barbra,
[FRENCH CAPTAIN A]
We march!
Saint Barbara, defend our King!
[FRENCH SOLDIERS] Saint Barbara,
defend our King!
Saint Barbara, defend our King!
[JOSEPH] I'll see you safe,
Lady Maria. And then...
[PRIAPUS]
Then Joseph looked at me,
and said he'd come back soon
and save you for sure!
[MARIA laughs]
That fool boy.
What does he think he can
accomplish in battle?
I guess men will
ever play the fools,
when Ares beckons them forth.
[PRIAPUS] Master. Is your
magic still sealed away?
[MARIA]
I think. [grunts]
Seems so. Why has it not
yet returned to me?
[PRIAPUS]
Worry not, Maria.
Truly, there's still
plenty of time.
Viv will come flying in here
with the whole Guild!
Artemis went to go
get them and they--
[banging]
[PRIAPUS]
What's that sound?
[FRENCH INQUISITION MEN]
Heave-ho!
[FEMALE A]
If you're burned in the flames,
how will your soul find
its way to Heaven?
[FEMALE B] The Inquisition
came to a fast verdict!
[MALE A] To be sure,
they fear the witch.
[FEMALE C] I think
they wanted this farce
to be over and done with.
[MALE B] There's no
telling when the witch
will use her magic and
make good her escape.
[MALE C]
A man in the market said
she would take normal people and
turn them into her thralls!
[FEMALE D]
Will you or not, it's decided.
She'll burn on the morrow.
[PRIAPUS]
On the morrow? Oh, no!
The flames?
On the morrow?
[PRIAPUS]
Stay put!
I'll go find Artemis and see
what's taking her so long!
[MARIA]
Priapus!
Don't go.
Le Comte's wishes
are quite clear.
Yet, still, his judgment was
rendered in great haste.
He doesn't risk the witch
regaining her power.
[GILBERT] Like as not, His Noble
Self wishes to make known
his own powers.
But I am the Magistrate.
By rights, it is my decision to
condemn the witch to the flames.
[FRENCH INQUISITION CAPTAIN A]
The result is the same.
[GILBERT]
And the choice is still mine.
I referenced many texts
on the Inquisition law.
This path holds most true.
What of Frere Bernard's wishes?
I thought he'd taken
interest in the witch.
Frere Bernard is...
no longer a concern.
[ARTEMIS] There's no time to
lose. We must fly now!
[PRIAPUS]
Then let's make haste!
But, what of Viv?
She only just drank my elixir.
It's like to keep her dreaming
until tomorrow evening
at the earliest.
[PRIAPUS] But they'll be
done with it by then!
What of the other witches?
[EDWINA] I'm afraid I
couldn't reach them.
[PRIAPUS]
Then it must fall to you!
[EDWINA gasps]
[PRIAPUS]
Please, help us save Maria!
There's no way!
[PRIAPUS] I'll do anything
you want! I swear, on my soul!
--Take my body!
--[EDWINA screams]
Claim me! I'm yours!
Take your pleasure from me!
Would you just shut
up for a second?
But, I don't know
how else to help!
Stop with the excuses.
Now, Edwina!
What can I do? Saint Michael
is hunting down witches!
Even Viv couldn't
face the Archangel!
Artemis. I'm just
not ready to die.
Edwina. Please, you must
[EDWINA]
I-I'm not... I can't.
Then I'm sorry to have bothered
you. Tend well to Viv.
[EDWINA gasps]
We will do what we can to save
her, but this isn't the end.
Witches are no
longer secure here.
They won't stop hunting you.
Please be safe, Edwina.
I'm sorry. What else would you
expect of a coward like me?
[EZEKIEL grunting]
[MARIA]
Ezekiel.
[EZEKIEL] I called
upon Ann and Martha.
And how is the latter faring?
[EZEKIEL]
Martha is suffering.
She feels that she's
betrayed you.
She should not
torment herself.
[EZEKIEL]
She and Ann are scared for you!
[MARIA] I wish I could
see them but once more.
[EZEKIEL]
You can see them!
All you must do is ask
forgiveness of Heaven.
Forgiveness.
[EZEKIEL] It's that simple,
Maria! But a few words.
Then all will be as it should!
I'm sorry.
[gasps]
[MARIA]
I can't, Ezekiel.
They're only words.
The effort of a moment!
I just can't do it.
What does that even mean?!
[MARIA] If I say it, I'll no
longer be myself, Ez
[EZEKIEL whimpers]
May God be with you.
[gasps] Farewell Maria.
Farewell.
[EDWINA] Where are you going?
You can't be up yet!
This is sheer madness, Viv!
I have to try! She has my
dream, Edwina. She has...
[EDWINA]
Viv!
[VIV]
Edwina. I--
[EDWINA] Please, don't
force me to choose!
[RÉGLISSE coos]
[EDWINA gasps]
[meow]
[CERNUNNOS] The witch cast upon
the pyre by those she saved
and those she failed to save.
Her path is choked
in smoke and fire.
Witch Maria. In this hour,
what thinkst thou?
[MARIA] Always war.
Why have I always sought
to put an end to war?
Why do I hate it so?
Did I simply wish for
people to adore me?
To praise me for saving
innocent lives?
Who am I?
What have I ever
truly wanted?
Joseph.
Men of France!
When those walls fall,
that castle lay before
us like a feast!
With emboldened steel,
send those Englishmen
straight to hell!
Seek out wealth and righteous
glory, and it will be found!
Fight well!
The bastards of
Briton will nev--
[horse whinnies]
[VILLAGERS murmur]
[FEMALE E] That filthy
witch will be judged.
[MALE D]
Accursed heretic.
[FEMALE F] See the way she
looks at us with such malice.
[MALE E] She's a heathen,
sure enough.
[MARIA]
All these people.
Everyone... came to see
the witch punished.
Do they hate me? Fear me?
Why do they stare at me so?
[FRENCH SOLDIERS yell]
[ENGLISH SOLDIERS yell]
Release!
Those Britons grow bolder!
I demand that you
destroy that gate!
[FRENCH SOLDIERS groan]
[FRENCH VASSAL A]
Our footmen cannot
approach the city, my lord.
We must sunder the ramparts
if we're to claim victory.
Send a message to
the cannons, then!
Bring the full strength
of the bombard to bear!
[GILBERT]
Maria of the Forest.
Here, in the sight of God,
may your heathen soul
be cleansed in fire.
[FRENCH INQUISITION CAPTAIN A]
Shall we grant mercy, Brother?
[GILBERT] She has earned this.
Now, tie her to the stake.
[ARTEMIS] I'll create a
commotion while you untie Maria.
[PRIAPUS] Why should you be
the one to dive in there?
[ARTEMIS]
They'd kill you.
[PRIAPUS] Maybe so, but...
I'd die to save her.
[ARTEMIS]
You idiot. We'll go together.
Lady Maria, grant me strength.
I will win your freedom
upon this day!
Hear me, Le Comte! I bring
news from the cannonade!
The Cambier Mons Meg
is ready to fire.
We await your command to light!
Ha, ha! Excellent! Let this
salvo be the last they hear!
Saint Barbara,
defend us this day!
[FRENCH SOLDIERS panting]
[FRENCH SOLDIERS grunting]
Fire!
[FRENCH SOLDIERS cheer]
Ride forth!
[FRENCH SOLDIER E]
Men of France! Forward!
Heh. Better to flee, Joseph.
Foolish. I was such a...
a fool in the end--
[coughs]
[ARTEMIS]
Let's go save our master!
[PRIAPUS]
Right!
What the...?
Who... is that?
That light.
Is she a fellow witch?
[EDWINA grunts]
My body's definitely not used
to flying like that anymore.
Curse you, daylight.
Why are you so bright?
Edwina. It's you.
I came for thee. What are you
doing tied up on that pyre?
I won't let you get burned!
Huh?
[EDWINA] If you let yourself
get caught this easy,
no witch is going
to be respected!
What if the Church starts a
new witch hunt after this?
I don't follow.
People's fear and respect for
witches is how we stay safe!
Seize her at once.
Yes, at once.
Soldiers to the fore!
[FRENCH INQUISITION MEN clamor]
[EDWINA]
Belisama, now! Grant me fire!
Archers! Take aim!
[ARTEMIS]
Thank goodness you're here.
Edwina!
Get her down from there!
[EDWINA] Raise up shields!
Tarvos Trigaranos!
I need your strength
a little longer!
I swear one of the witches
will make amends!
With all this magic I really
hope Saint Michael
is looking elsewhere
at the moment.
[RÉGLISSE]
The shield's fading, Master!
[gasps]
[MARIA]
Edwina!
[EDWINA] I've already come this
far to save your life, Maria.
I may as well use all I have!
Nantosuelta!
Lend me your fires!
[VILLAGERS scream]
Heathen witches!
You dare flout the Church!
[GILBERT gasps]
[EDWINA] We can find refuge
at my house for now.
[MARIA]
Take me to the battlefield.
[ALL]
What?
[EDWINA]
To the battlefield?
But Miss Maria. Your magic
power still hasn't come back.
There's still a war going on.
And I intend to stop it.
[ENGLISH, FRENCH SOLDIERS
shouting]
[ENGLISH GIRL cries]
[GALFA grunts]
So are you hoping to find some
nice loot in the cathedral, boy?
Or maybe you're
just here to hide?
I came to find glory worthy
of Lady Maria's freedom!
But now I stare upon foul
inequity made flesh!
[GALFA] I haven't got any
pretty words for you, Joseph.
Only steel.
[JOSEPH gasps]
[EDWINA sighs]
Or, just go.
What a spine she's got.
I've hated your eyes from the
first time they looked at me!
[FRENCH BEARER CHIEF]
She's stealing the bombard!
Look at them scramble
about. Like ants.