It's been too long, Uncle.
You've become quite a
man of the cloth, my boy.
You bring honor to the family.
[BERNARD] Would you care
for some apple cider?
It's our best.
Very well.
Now, what is this all about?
Uncle, you are both my blood and
Le Comte Guillaume as well.
I come to you as a petitioner
about the witch, Maria.
[sighs]
I should have guessed.
[GUILLAUME]
So, the witch.
[BERNARD]
Yes.
Her battlefield antics leave
the common folk feeling
unsure about the war.
[GUILLAUME]
She has been expanding
her sphere of influence.
[BERNARD]
You are a wise man, Uncle.
I'm sure a noble of
your great experience
has already weighed
the issue of Maria.
[GUILLAUME]
Indeed.
She sows chaos at every turn.
Meanwhile, the war
empties the King's coffers,
and he taxes us
all the worse for it.
[BERNARD]
And with every halted battle,
she drags us further
into this stalemate.
Without a clear victor
at the end of the day,
war is but a senseless butchery.
[GUILLAUME]
Well put, Nephew.
If only we could loose her
upon England's forces alone.
[gasps]
Oh yes, of course.
That's it.
[GUILLAUME]
Hmm?
[BERNARD]
We shall take this thorn,
and drive it into
our foe's side.
Will she obey?
[BERNARD] Surely not,
but if we feed her word
of England's maneuvers
deftly enough,
she'll think she acts
of her own volition.
[GUILLAUME]
Hmm. If she takes the bait,
wouldn't the peasantry love
her all the more for it?
[BERNARD]
They do not love her, Uncle.
They tolerate her,
because she serves a purpose.
End the war,
remove that purpose,
and they will cast her out.
Well, it's a bold gambit.
[BERNARD]
You are the man for it.
Huh?
[BERNARD]
She can weaken England,
but we'll need a
God-fearing noble,
a count, perhaps,
to deliver the coup de grace.
[GUILLAUME] Hm. And I
assume that's where I step in.
As faithful servant of the King
and stout-hearted Christian.
We appear at the endgame.
We crush the remnants
of England's forces and the
witch in one fell swoop.
[BERNARD]
Le Comte Guillaume,
only you can lead
the King to victory.
The heavens
themselves will sing
at the sight of this
most righteous deed.
Tis' a heady brew
you've poured me, Nephew.
But, I mean, would it
be acceptable?
The girl is a witch.
[BERNARD]
Get upon your knees.
[GUILLAUME]
Huh?
Please, my uncle.
[GUILLAUME grunts]
Ego te absolvo. Your sins
are forgiven, and will be.
[GALFA] So, lost your
taste for the fight?
[JOSEPH] Le Comte
Guillaume has bade me serve
as messenger again.
Yeah, well, keep that
fancy gear handy.
[JOSEPH]
Huh?
[GALFA]
Take a look around.
[JOSEPH]
I see my lord's camp. Why?
[GALFA]
He's gathering mercenaries.
Rumor has it the ol'
Jew-sti-se himself,
Richemont, is going to
send in his ordinance.
Ain't that a pisser?
[GALFA laughs] And none of
this is news to you, right?
I, uh.
Hell, I know you'd
tell me if you could.
At the least we can finally
bloody their nose a bit.
[JOSEPH sighs] You keep an
ear to the ground, don't you?
[GALFA]
Damn straight.
Going into battle not knowing
what you're up against
is a good way to wind up dead.
Huh?
[GALFA]
Hey, if it's a good fight,
I can finally pay you back
those coins I borrowed.
No need. Honestly.
[GALFA]
Shut up. I'm gonna do it.
Hey.
[GALFA] For now, here's a
token of my thanks.
Uh, that really isn't necessary.
[GALFA]
Tell me.
Yes?
When I was drunk, did I
tell you anything strange?
Uh, no, sir.
Well, nothing in particular.
Perfect.
[SUZANNE]
Say, Viv.
How did your talk with Maria go?
[VIV] Well, Rome wasn't
built in a day.
She's going to join
the guild, though, right?
That was the whole point of it.
She said she'd rather be alone.
No wonder she's not making
any headway with the gentlemen.
C'est vrai?
There is this one boy
who calls on her a lot
[RÉGLISSE meows]
You see? Even Edwina's
cat's in the know.
Half a moment, you're not
talking about Priapus, are you?
The poor lil' he-owl
without a beak?
I believe that he serves
one of the local noblemen.
Yeah?
The virgin's doing
pretty well for herself.
Is it me, or does
Joseph come by a lot?
And usually on horseback.
His master keeps
him busy, I guess.
[ARTEMIS] Oui, even though
all the quarrels that he brings
are just petty ones,
They keep piling up.
[PRIAPUS] Getting through them
all still runs Maria ragged.
Hold on! She told me she was
stepping out for some air!
I get it! She's out
there meddling!
I was just kidding!
No way she could she do that
with you watching over her!
You really had me going
there for a moment.
[ARTEMIS]
Huh...
Another one. More minor
requests than ever.
I'm sorry.
I know Saint Michael has
forbade you to use your magic.
It pains me to tempt you thus,
but my lord commands me hither.
Please don't fret.
You were right to bring them.
[JOSEPH] Milady,
these petitions are minor,
but maybe we inch closer
to peace with each one.
I hope that you're right.
--[JOSEPH] Also.
--[MARIA] Huh?
So, regarding Archangel Michael.
[MARIA]
Ugh.
[JOSEPH]
Any sign?
Pas de rien.
The world is tumultuous.
He's probably
forgotten all about me.
[JOSEPH]
Would that it were so.
Milady, if I may be of use
to you in any sort of regard,
you need but say the word.
Maybe I will.
By the way.
Go on.
[MARIA] Before, you mentioned
us inching closer to peace.
Once we finally
get there, then what?
My Lady?
[MARIA]
Are you dense?
I'm trying to ask you what
you want to do with your life.
It's funny. As of late,
people keep asking me that.
You see, I've served
Le Comte Guillaume
ever since I was a boy,
so this is all I know.
I suppose I would serve my lord
in times of peace,
much as ever I have.
Ah, I see.
[JOSEPH] One day, I will take
a wife, and have children.
Something like
Ann's family, like as not.
And what does the
future hold for you?
Hold on! For me?
[JOSEPH]
Yes.
More of the same,
I guess! I'm a witch!
It doesn't matter what's
going on in the world.
That's my role no matter what.
[ARTEMIS]
Watching these two fumble about
sets my talons on edge.
Oh? I find their
innocence quite endearing.
I believe she should
join with this boy
in holy matrimony and
live out a simple life.
And relinquish all her
powers in the process.
Her magic is an
abomination unto the Lord.
Its loss would be
nothing to mourn.
[PRIAPUS]
What?
[ARTEMIS]
Ezekiel!
[gasps]
Go on!
I've never seen Heaven,
but this world is held together
by the pure and profane alike.
[EZEKIEL]
Uh...
[YVAIN]
Listen up, you lucky bastards!
Maria's been vexing
the English so much,
they don't know their
heads from their asses!
We've been hired
to cut them down
the next time they're fool
enough to show themselves!
Best part of all,
you get paid in advance!
Half right now,
the rest if you're not
feeding a buzzard at the end.
And of course,
the money's on top of whatever
you can grab off the Brits!
[MERCENARY A]
Yay, Captain!
[YVAIN]
That ain't all!
We've got drink, courtesy of
his Lordship the Count!
So raise some hell,
you mongrels!
You've earned it!
[MERCENARIES]
♪Trum...trum...♪
♪trum-pa-da-bum...♪
♪Going to the grave
with coins in hand,♪
♪make we no reprimand.♪
♪The Reaper take his due,
no matter where we die,♪
♪it matters not to I.♪
♪O, Lady Fortune, deal my hand,
whether ghastly or grand.♪
Hey, Lolotte.
Have you seen Galfa
anywhere around?
He stumbled away and three
sheets to the wind, sir.
I see.
Be careful not to open
your heart to that one.
He's made a name
of breaking them.
'Course I won't.
And that is not what
I've been opening.
[YVAIN laughs]
It's him I should worry about!
[MERCENARY E]
Other way, Galfa!
That's the cavalry's
encampment, you big drunk!
[GALFA]
Yeah, I got it!
Huh?
[MERCENARIES]
♪For liquor and a lass,♪
♪they both're just the thing,♪
[sighs]
Looks like being a knight
gets ya a fine-looking doxy.
[CERNUNNOS]
You depart?
[MARIA yelps]
[CERNUNNOS]
Why do you slip into the night?
Tell me, what's wrong
with ending the war?
[CERNUNNOS] Have you thought
about this peace you so crave?
What?
[CERNUNNOS]
Witch Maria,
you hasten your
own obsolescence.
When the final
sword is sheathed,
they will all forget you.
Is this the outcome you desire?
[MARIA] I hate the fighting,
so I'm trying to end it!
Who cares about the rest?
[GALFA grunts]
How much did I drink?
Good morrow Galfa.
Yeah sure, and,
what's your name?
You forgot?
After all the fun we had?
[EUGÉNIE, GALFA gasp]
[GALFA]
Huh?
J-Jean!
[JEAN] What is the meaning
of this, Eugénie?
I was about to
say Eugénie, y'know.
Mon Dieu.
[GALFA grunting]
This is a damnable nuisance.
What counsel can you
offer me, Nephew?
You already know what
must be done, my uncle.
Do you think I'd ask if the
matter were that simple?
[GALFA groans]
[GUILLAUME]
Cuckolded by a mercenary.
--The knight is furious.
--[JEAN growls]
[gasps]
[GUILLAUME]
However, I've no doubt executing
the letch will destroy
morale among his brethren.
Was it a man of the
Red Arm Brothers?
[GUILLAUME]
Yes.
But we can't appear to favor
them, lest the Imperial Cavalry
make trouble for us down
the road with the King.
Is there a way to see
this dilemma resolved
without giving offence
to either man's faction?
There is.
[GUILLAUME]
Hm?
It's simple, really.
We'll have the two
fight a formal duel.
[growls]
[MERCENARY F]
Hey, who're you betting on?
[MERCENARY G]
Normally, Galfa would
have the upper hand, but...
He's down to just the one.
[MERCENARY F laughs]
It's the day after next.
The duel will be held at the
Imperial Cavalry's encampment.
I have been chosen to
serve as the witness.
[GALFA]
I see. Tough break.
[grunts]
Oh, hush! I know
it hurts, ya damn fool.
Stop waving it about,
why don't ya!
[LOLOTTE giggles]
[GALFA scoffs]
Yeah.
Odds are two to eight
that you're taking a trip
to the boneyard, Galfa.
If you die, though,
I'll waive what you owe me.
Piss off!
[JOSEPH]
This duel.
[YVAIN, GALFA]
Huh?
It's barbaric.
[JOSEPH] Even if you win, you'll
be a marked man to the knights.
Leave this place,
for now at least.
Make haste to your home--
Where's that, huh?
I got no home in
France or elsewhere.
[JOSEPH]
Huh?
That shouldn't come
as a surprise, boy.
How many Galfas have you met?
He might've come here under
the same circumstances.
[JOSEPH]
But, what of Galfa's ambitions?
[GALFA]
Huh?
[YVAIN]
This one? That's a laugh.
[gasps]
[GALFA grunts]
A word, if ya please?
[GALFA] Guess I said
more than ya let on.
[JOSEPH]
Forgive me.
[GALFA]
It's fine,
but don't bring it up
in front of other folks.
Yes sir. But, I still
feel the same.
Escape with your life.
You're planning to
become a knight and king--
[GALFA, JOSEPH grunt]
Over the years, I've been
called a lot of things,
but no man has ever
called me coward.
I'm stayin'.
Dying for the sake of your pride
is nothing but foolishness!
Every day, men die for less!
The choice is mine,
right or wrong!
[JOSEPH gasps]
[GALFA]
But, it means a lot knowing
somebody don't want me dead.
Thank you.
[MARIA]
Have a seat.
C'mon, you're making me nervous.
[EZEKIEL]
Hmph.
Uh, all right.
You're not here for...
Le Comte, are you?
Milady... I'm here.
Go on.
[JOSEPH] Because my
friend is about to die.
[gasps]
[JOSEPH] Well, he may yet
survive this but, I doubt it.
[ARTEMIS]
Huh. Guess he came for advice.
[JOSEPH] I told him that he
should run away while he can,
but he refuses to
save his own life.
I think it's important to him
to stare oblivion
square in the eye.
I don't want his dreams
to go unfulfilled!
Milady, you and he are the
most resolute people I know.
Tell me, please.
How do you possess such an
inner wellspring of strength?
Don't look at me
with that face.
I'm not getting on the
wrong side of the knights
because you wet your wick.
[GALFA]
Goes without sayin'.
So, how you gonna
get outta this one?
You're wrong about me, Joseph.
I'm not strong at all.
Huh?
[MARIA] No matter
how many battles I stop,
the war continues.
Sometimes.
those whose lives I've
saved try to kill each other.
and I think, "What could
that possibly accomplish?"
[sighs]
But then, whenever
they look at me,
they're probably asking
themselves the same thing.
[JOSEPH]
Huh?
[MARIA] They see a girl who
keeps trying to stop the war.
I must bewilder them so.
It's such a conundrum.
One I'll have to get
figured out someday.
How can people
understand each other?
Who knows?
Yeah. All I can do
is believe in myself.
I think the same is
true of your friend.
And, really, it's true of
us all. Well, kind of.
How so?
Because, if you
make up your mind,
you stick to it!
You just put your head down and
keep at it until you're done!
Easy, right?
Ah, I do see what you mean.
[EZEKIEL sighs] Watching her
fumble through that moment
was so painful.
[ARTEMIS]
I think we're all.
[PRIAPUS]
Of one mind on that.
It's almost tomorrow.
Thanks for your help.
I know I was a burden on ya.
Don't be stupid, Galfa.
These days, there ain't much
I won't do for a flash of gold.
Speaking of gold, right now,
it's nine-to-one odds
you're going to lose.
That's a hell of a way
to make some money,
bettin' on a life. Ain't it?
[MERCENARY H]
Get to the fighting!
Will this really bolster
the mercenaries' morale?
If not, throw them some coins.
That should suffice.
[GUILLAUME]
Hm.
Will this fight truly
be to the death?
[BERNARD] The cavalry would
never have agreed to it if not.
Revenge cuts a better
figure when clad
in a mantle of pageantry.
[JEAN]
Hah! What a wretched opponent!
This victory will
bring me no honor.
If he's so wretched,
how come you're mounted
and wearing a full set of plate?
[ALL laugh]
[JEAN growls]
[YVAIN] Fetch the
knight a crossbow!
Then we'll see some heroics!
[JEAN]
Enough!
I deign to fight
on equal footing.
But, I still have two
good arms to his one.
[GALFA]
Mouthy bastard.
And if the mercenary should
somehow win, then what?
Come what may,
this trial by combat will
be the end of the matter.
You might last for
a moment, perhaps.
I did what I could.
Now it's on Galfa.
This will be good.
By the rights given to Le Comte
from the King of France,
this day, before God,
the knight Jean de Drouant
and the mercenary Galfa seek
your judgment via combat.
Step forward, each of you,
and lay your hand
atop the Bible.
State your petition,
to Heaven and Earth alike!
[JEAN]
Hear me, Galfa.
I swear, by the
words of our Lord.
I will avenge the
outrages of the flesh
you have wrought upon
my love, Eugénie.
Only by force have
you known her favor.
[GALFA] It's true enough
that I approached her,
but she shrugged out of her
clothes just as quick as I did.
You lie!
Gentlemen, please!
By the consent of both,
they give their
quarrel up to God!
Through this duel, the Heavens
will illumine the wronged party.
May the righteous man prevail!
I will serve as the official
witness of the duel to come.
Begin!
[yells]
[GALFA grunts]
[MERCENARY I]
Cut 'em to shreds!
[MERCENARY J]
Stop fooling around, Galfa!
Hurry up an' die already!
[FRENCH KNIGHT A]
No respect for dueling!
[FRENCH KNIGHT B]
They fight for pay.
Of course they're
lacking in piety.
[grunts]
Without his other arm,
he's got no chance.
He can't win.
[GALFA panting]
[yells]
[grunts]
Ah! It looks as
though our problem's
about to be solved.
[VIV] You're not going to
stop the fight this time?
[MARIA]
Viv?
Maybe the one with the
hurt arm strikes your fancy.
Him? Of course not!
--[metal clangs]
--[JOSEPH gasps]
[grunts]
Hey, friend. I got
a lot riding on this.
So, hurry up and die already!
[GALFA grunting]
Say, should some fights be
allowed to run their course?
[VIV]
Huh?
[JEAN, GALFA grunting]
Looks like the mercenary's
holding his own.
How odd.
Huh?
[grunts]
[gasps]
[FRENCH KNIGHT C]
Jean's victorious. Good.
It took long enough.
--Do it!
--Hey!
--Kill him already!
--That's it for you, Galfa!
[JEAN]
And now,
I split your worthless
face asunder.
Wait! Please, just don't!
I'm sorry! God, forgive me!
[JEAN] You have
acted like a beast.
Fitting, then, that you
shall die like one!
[gasps]
How could I have
been so blind?
[GALFA]
Go for the kill.
Swing that sword
as hard as you can!
You damn fool!
[JEAN]
It can't be!
--[GALFA yells]
--[JEAN grunts]
Tricky little bastard!
He swung his arm just in time!
That's our Galfa.
[GALFA chuckles]
What? A sword breaker?
[JEAN grunts]
[GALFA yells]
[JEAN grunting]
[GALFA]
Who's the beast now, huh?
[JEAN screams]
No. He'll kill him!
That's unexpected.
[JEAN, GALFA grunting]
Stop the duel!
[gasps]
[GILBERT]
Heaven has picked a champion!
Did I fulfill my obligation?
Tell me, damn you!
[CROWD cheering, booing]
What say you?
Did I give him a fight?
[cheering, booing continues]
Just look at 'em.
[LOLOTTE giggles]
Thank goodness.
[scoffs]
He shamed us all.
Yes, he did.
But now, all we can
do is bite our tongues.
And once again,
the Lord gives me
much proof that his will
is well-nigh inscrutable.
Rejoice, Galfa.
You will serve,
though you know it not.
[VIV] Tell the truth.
That fight down there.
You were about to
break it up, right?
[MARIA]
Obviously. Why?
[laughs]
God, you're adorable!
Huh?
[JOSEPH]
Are you all right?
[GALFA] Seein' as
how I had Yvain bet
all that money on
my long-shot win,
I've never been better, kid!
It's what I borrowed
and then some.
Guess I owe that
knight my thanks.
[gasps]
Haven't you heard yet?
Sir Jean de Drouant--
[GALFA]
He killed himself.
[JOSEPH]
Yes.
The jeering from his comrades
was more than he could bear.
[GALFA] That's what comes
from caring what people think.
[JOSEPH] His lady seems
to have disappeared
in the wake of all this.
[GALFA]
Hmm.
[JOSEPH]
Do you know where she's gone?
And why the hell
would I know?
Sure ain't like we
pledged our troth.
She probably went
back to her homeland.
I do remember her saying
how beautiful it was there.
That kind of girl,
she should have never
come to a place like this.
I wonder if it's so
different there.
Tell me something.
Uh-huh?
Earlier.
I wanna know who you
bet on to win the duel?
Huh? As witness,
I couldn't wager.
[GALFA] Yeah, fine,
but what if you had?
I would've put it
all on you, Galfa.
You gotta learn how
to lie better, kid.
You're the one who said I
should run away, remember?
[JOSEPH]
Ah... You're right.
[GALFA]
Uh-huh.
"Hang on tight" doesn't
mean to smother me!
It's really a bother.
As I learn more,
I will pass it along.
[MARIA]
You're so mean, Joseph.
Glory unto God
and Vive la France!