[MICHAEL]
Tell me the truth, Maria,
have you really abandoned
the happiness of others
in the pursuit of your
own pleasure?
[MARIA laughs]
Hardly. Listen. I came to
learn something important
about the workings
of this world.
There was little point in my
trying to grant happiness
to others until I
found it for myself.
It's not about one or the other.
It's about attaining both.
What kind of reasoning is that?!
[MARIA]
You didn't say that I'm wrong.
This answer you
have given me.
Does it reflect your heart?
Yes.
Nonetheless, you have continued
to rebel most brazenly
against the will
of the Almighty.
[JOSEPH gasps]
[MICHAEL] The balance of this
world must be maintained.
Archangel Michael.
I should have guessed.
Our love didn't get
much time to blossom.
I'll have the god of
wind fly you to safety,
so at least I know you're
well away from here.
But, what of--?
[MARIA]
Survive.
[MARIA gasps]
[ARTEMIS]
Maria!
[PRIAPUS]
Are you all right?
[MARIA]
How did you...?
[VIV]
Listen, love.
[MARIA gasps]
It'd be a bloody shame for
you to die mere moments
after you finally land a man.
Scamper off to some corner,
and let us take care of Michael.
[MARIA]
Wait, what?
You came all the way up
here just to say that?
[EDWINA] I just wanted
to stay at home, but no!
This feud's become a problem for
witches both near and far!
[RÉGLISSE]
Meow!
You don't mean to
say you're going to
lift your hand
against Michael!
[ARTEMIS]
You're not alone!
[PRIAPUS]
You've us as well!
What?
Please stop!
You cannot hold back the
whirlwind with mere numbers!
Only one...
...way to find out!
Give him a run...
...for his money!
[JOSEPH gasps]
[ALL]
Hear us, O matronly Rosmerta!
With Mercurius, lend your power
to we humble witches
of the hearth!
[EZEKIEL growls]
[gasps]
Just in time.
[BELLA] We heard that the Church
was giving Maria trouble.
Having more people
side with Michael
when it comes to witches
is the last thing we need.
They're gonna think
we're milquetoasts
if we don't fight back.
Don't look shocked
that we're here.
[MARIA]
What?
[BELLA]
You're stubborn as a mule,
but you're our mule,
for right or wrong.
[MARIA gasps]
[VIV laughs]
Witches and beasts
of time immemorial,
do you truly mean to throw
the world into disarray?
Piss off!
[EZEKIEL gasps]
[VIV] I'm sick to death
of this, Michael!
Stop nattering on about balance
and tell me what you think!
Viv. Perhaps you should
strike a lighter tone--
I want to know if there's a
brain in that head of yours.
Or are you a puppet?
Hold on! Peace, Michael!
Forgive her cutting words!
I don't want you getting
involved, all right?
Huh? But fighting for you is
the whole reason we're here!
[MARIA]
I know that!
But I hate battles, and this is
shaping up to be an epic one!
Good on you, holding
true to your ideals.
That said. I think there'll
be a fight either way.
[MARIA]
Huh.
Michael wait! Stand down!
[VIV]
Edwina?
[EDWINA]
Well, in for a penny!
You attack a herald of Heaven!
[CHANTAL] Tell him to leave
witches alone already!
Everyone, just stop!
I didn't want this!
[GILBERT] Brother Bernard,
we should be scouring
the countryside for those
damned heretics.
In light of Maria's escape.
I don't understand why
you're so eager to bring
your scrolls to the abbot?
[BERNARD]
What good is an epiphany
kept to one's self, Brother?
[BERNARD] With time enough
to ruminate upon this,
I believe we can come to
understand Almighty God
in an entirely new light.
[GILBERT]
"New light?"
[BERNARD] Gilbert, when we
naught but murmur the words of
old to our flock, have we served
our Father in good stead?
No. 'Tis a waste of our talents.
We are adept creations, and
to enfeeble ourselves is a sin.
We were granted
precious reason,
and the urge to
better ourselves.
[BERNARD] This precept, is
unique in the history of man.
The Heavenly Host is
a superfluous entity.
[GILBERT gasps]
What are you suggesting?
[BERNARD] Merely that
we are the masters here.
Earth is meant to reflect
our will, not that of God.
[GILBERT]
We, the masters?
[BERNARD]
Of course!
[GILBERT]
Brother!
[BERNARD]
Reasoning will be nurtured
with the irrationality
that God provides.
In a way, we can flourish even
without the divine
protection of God.
Who would've thought
that a witch would serve
as fulcrum to my
mind? Bless that girl!
I asked a painter to
immortalize her with his arts,
that all may know her! Maria!
[MARIA]
Viv! Edwina!
[gasps] Joseph! What do you
think you're doing? Run away!
Never!
[MARIA gasps]
[JOSEPH] I remain!
Even at the cost of my soul!
[MICHAEL]
So be it. Ezekiel.
Transfix them both.
I cannot!
Spear of Heaven. You would
flout the will of God?
Master, you bade me watch,
and I have done so.
Whatever I've learned about
humanity and its virtues
during my time on Earth,
it is all thanks to
Maria's influence.
She's possessed of a
righteous heart, Master!
Ezekiel.
Tell me. Wherefore does this
heretic hold you in such thrall?
[bell tolls]
[MICHAEL]
Witch Maria.
Almighty God now demands
a reckoning of your deeds.
[gasps]
[EZEKIEL groans]
[MICHAEL] Any whom the
witch's acts have touched.
Heed my holy summons that
God may have His answer.
In your eyes,
what is this Maria?
She is a demon.
She steals my victories at
the cost of many a life.
She even lured my vassal Joseph.
[JOSEPH]
Milord Guillaume.
[GUILLAUME] Lord may
devils bear her hence.
[ENGLISH SOLDIER A]
Maria?
She's a useful ally, but when
she's your enemy, look out.
[FRENCH SOLDIER A]
She saved my life.
What's going on?
Archangel Michael is powerful.
He's giving voice
to the thoughts they
hold in their hearts.
Really? Impressive,
even for an angel!
Indeed. Their thoughts
are laid open before us
like the pages of a ledger.
We can hear them, but they
cannot hear us in turn.
[MARIA gasps]
That's amazing. Wow.
[VIV] He'd have drubbed
us no matter what.
[MARIA]
Viv?
[EDWINA]
So now you see reason!
[GALFA]
Huh? What do I think of her?
That girl is like
a slow death.
Everything worth a damn,
she ripped away from me.
My loot. Glory. My shield arm.
And the one man
I called my friend.
Believe me. I've had my
fill of her for a lifetime.
Soon as we get our pay from the
Count, we're shut of this place.
[GILBERT] The witch Maria
is a loathsome creature.
A harlot who dares to spit
in the face of our Lord!
When at last she's set ablaze...
[MICHAEL] I see. Bernard.
What is the witch to you?
[BERNARD whimpers]
It can't be.
The Archangel, made visible to
man, engaging in conversation.
This is... This is calamitous!
Bernard! The words you
speak are apostasy!
[BERNARD] This flies in
the face of my precepts!
For the sake of man's
advancement.
Humans must foreswear the
words of all but their fellows!
Not even angels
on high! No!
Not even the voice
of God. Himself!
Do not touch him!
Mankind!
Mankind doesn't
need you anymore!
Whatever the Church's position,
my opinion of Maria
is the same as that.
I don't know.
She did save the village.
Hard to see the evil
in a person like her.
[ANN] It doesn't matter
what anyone says!
'Cause! I like her!
And Artemis and Priapus
and Dovey, too!
The name's Ezekiel.
[MARTHA]
What is Maria to me?
[gasps]
She is a witch of great power,
as well as a treasured friend.
A witch can be so dear to you?
[MARTHA] Yes. Not just of
late, but over the many years.
We've argued, as
friends are wont to do,
but most of our time was spent
in laughter or in tears,
the likes of which one can
only shed in the company
of a boon companion like her.
And yet, like Peter,
I denied her.
But, the moment that stone left
my hand, I realized something.
Maria will always
be a part of my life.
She's woven up tight in
the tapestry of my heart.
[MARTHA] I know
you're listening, Maria.
I hope that you can
forgive me, dear.
I do!
[MICHAEL]
Speak, young man.
Many have borne witness,
but what is Maria... to you?
There, was a man.
A hermit, who lived
deep in the woods.
He spoke of a future
full of peace.
Pax Dei.
The Peace of God.
A man heard my voice
many years ago,
and sought to bring about
this world without conflict.
Huh?
[MICHAEL] Stand you as
inheritor to his dream?
So, he toiled in
service of Heaven.
France has been locked
in war since before my birth.
To my ear, a world at peace
rang true as a fairy tale.
Even if such a
thing could exist.
God seemed little inclined to
grant such ease to His children.
[VALKYRIE A]
He is stouthearted.
Should they die, he'll make a
fine addition to our ranks.
[JOSEPH] Yes. I let such
thoughts bedew my mind,
never once lifting a
finger in their service.
But then, I met a girl who
lived her convictions.
The scales have fallen from
mine eyes, Saint Michael.
I know now what I need to do.
I desire nothing more than
to champion such ideals
by her side.
Though we may leave these fair
environs far behind, we will--
--[ARTEMIS] Hm?
--[PRIAPUS] Huh?
[JOSEPH gasps]
[MARIA] What makes you think
I'm going anywhere?
But if you stay, the Church
may try to harry you further!
I'll not run. Not a chance!
It doesn't matter the cost.
I'll put an end to bloodshed
until the day that I die!
Michael's hearing every
word of this!
He could just decide to
kill you preemptively.
Speaking of! I've something
to say to you!
Whether I have
magic or not,
I'll stop every battle I come
across! I promise you that!
So if you're going
to smite me for that,
you might as well
do it right now!
Such a fool.
[MARIA] Y'know. I had some
time to mull things over,
being stuck in
a cell and all.
And I think maybe I'm starting
to see Heaven's point of view.
So. Give God a
message for me.
You let Him know, that just
this once, I forgive Him!
--[JOSEPH gasps]
--[EDWINA] You forgive?
I feel blasphemous but
hearing those words!
[MICHAEL]
Heh.
[EZEKIEL gasps]
[chuckles] You caught me
off-guard. That's very rare.
[MARIA laughs]
[VIV]
Michael laughed. Oh my God!
--[bell tolls]
--[ALL gasp]
For all of your irksome ways,
it seems you are now deemed
a part of the world's
natural balance.
The Heavenly Host will spurn
your words, and you, ours.
But know that it would gladden
our Father mightily if you and
He could exist in some
degree of understanding.
Of course, when you
threaten the balance
it remains my duty
to prevent you.
Mais oui. I'd hate for you
to have nothing left to do.
[MICHAEL] Hm. Thus I decree.
From this day forth,
the Heavenly Host shall think
upon Maria as a dear neighbor.
As such, we enjoin you all to
love thy neighbor as thyself,
and open your arms to her.
Heaven's injunction against this
child of magic has now ended.
[GILBERT gasping]
So, about that "neighbor" part.
[ARTEMIS] God forgives you.
That's the part that matters!
Oh, Maria! This
is such a relief!
[MICHAEL]
Ezekiel.
Master?
[MICHAEL] You have championed
a witch's cause,
in opposition to Heaven.
[EZEKIEL]
Yes, and my punishment?
This falls under
Gabriel's purview,
but God desires that I give
breath to His judgment.
Judgment? But she didn't--!
Hold your tongue.
[VIV] This is between the
Heavens and Ezekiel.
[MICHAEL] As one who has
fallen prey to free will,
you are fit to be
an angel no more.
You shall live as a human.
[EZEKIEL gasps]
[MARIA gasps]
[MICHAEL] Ezekiel, take what you
have learned of humanity,
and add to it as a
member of that which
you've grown to admire.
Almighty God offers
you a special kindness,
in exchange for your millennia
of unwavering fidelity.
You may choose your
mother-to-be.
[EZEKIEL gasps]
[ARTEMIS] Huh? She's
lookin' at you, Maria!
[MARIA]
Me?!
[ARTEMIS, PRIAPUS]
Mm-hm.
[VIV]
It's decided, then.
[MARIA] What? I can't just
be a mother! Right?
At least, you'd know
she's on the way.
[screams] So not only is God
pawning the dove off on me,
I'm going to lose
my powers as well?
If this is my forgiveness, I
prefer contempt, thank you!
[MICHAEL]
What say you, Ezekiel?
[MARIA] C'mon, Ezekiel! You
could do way better than me!
I don't want someone else.
[MARIA screams]
You'd let the poor dear be
born to some stranger woman,
is that it?
Well, it is the deal
everyone else gets!
Maria.
What about... you two?
I give up. Just know that I'm a
lot stricter than Saint Michael,
so you'd better not give me
any grief about it later.
You're gonna be
a cute baby.
[EZEKIEL cries]
See you soon, Mother.
[ARTEMIS]
Adieu for now, Ezekiel.
[PRIAPUS] Baby or not,
you had better remember us.
[MARIA]
Michael. Thank you.
[BELLA]
I guess we should be off, then.
[DOROTHÉE] Sorry to
have worn out our welcome
like this, Edwina.
[EDWINA] You can stay
longer, you know.
[SUZANNE]
Scared of Michael, are we?
Just because Heaven
forgave Maria
doesn't mean
we're in the clear.
Oh, come on. It's ages
since we attacked him.
I'm sure it's water
under the bridge.
If he meant to smite us,
he would've done so already.
[CHANTAL, DOROTHÉE]
Right?
[SUZANNE]
Shall we, ladies?
[RÉGLISSE]
Meow.
[VIV gasps]
[DOROTHÉE] We'll darken
your door again!
[EDWINA]
Be careful out there!
[CHANTAL]
You, too!
It was sort of pleasant having
the lot of them underfoot.
[VIV] I can't believe they
didn't tell me goodbye!
[EDWINA]
You slept too long.
I'm still getting over a spear
wound. It's a delicate junction,
you know. After I eat,
I'll be on my merry way.
The others are heading west,
if you want to try and catch up.
[VIV] Nothing doing, love.
England calls!
[EDWINA]
Huh?
[VIV] There should be a lot of
work for an enterprising witch,
right about now. Not to mention
lads to corrupt. Besides,
somebody should be striving
for peace over there.
[EDWINA] Peace is going
to be the death of us all.
[VIV laughs]
You think our Maria will keep
fighting the good fight?
[EDWINA]
How would I know?
She'll be all right.
After all, she's got him.
She's sorted, then!
Glad to hear it!
[GUILLAUME]
Are you serious?
[JOSEPH]
Yes. I serve a new master now.
I never believed that
you would slip off
to greener pastures
someday, Joseph.
But that look in your eye means
there's no dissuading you.
Huh?
[GUILLAUME]
Once you've made up your mind,
the Devil himself can't
hold you back.
Such willpower's a rarity
in one so young.
Milord, I... I don't
know what to say.
[sighs, chuckles]
God, you remind
me of your father.
I am forever in
your debt, sir.
[JOSEPH]
Le Comte said that we
should call upon him
from time to time.
[MARIA]
Huh? Me as well?
[JOSEPH]
Yes.
[MARIA]
Are you sure about that?
[MARIA gasps]
[CERNUNNOS] Departing to
the world of humans.
[MARIA]
I am.
[CERNUNNOS] The mantle of a
witch suits you no longer, then?
[MARIA] Far from it.
I'm me, no matter what.
And for anything that
I give up in this life,
I gain at least that
much newness in return.
[CERNUNNOS] Such as?
Let's see. I've flown from place
to place for as long as I
can remember, but when walking,
it's an adventure!
That's but a single example.
The greatest adventure
is yet to come.
[CERNUNNOS] You will live as one
whose name is lost to history?
Yes. Thank you again.
For what you told him that day.
[MICHAEL]
Speak, thou ancient colossus.
What is the witch Maria to you?
[CERNUNNOS] I am of the past,
and she is of the future.
Her time will end, as
mine has, but for now,
purpose burns bright within her.
This world is naught but the
accretion of all who have
come and gone, each
leaving their mark in turn.
Your Yahweh reigns
ascendant, Michael,
but even He is not immune
to the turning of the wheel.
When Maria happens to think
upon me, the faintest of wind
sweeps through the dust
of what I've become.
Do not sever my
last link to life.
You care to give
village life a try?
I should think it'll
beat sitting out here
all by your lonesome.
[CERNUNNOS]
Thank you, Maria, but no.
It shall suffice that you
merely remember me.
[MARIA] Well, at least take
my cottage, would you?
I think a warm hearth
could do you some good.
[CERNUNNOS]
I will consider it.
[MARIA]
Then see you around, Cernunnos.
[CERNUNNOS]
Yes. I daresay you shall.
I wonder, Joseph, will they even
let me enter the village?
I think you worry
too much, Maria.
But what if they don't?
I mean--
[ANN]
Hey!
[JOSEPH, MARIA]
Uh?
[ANN]
Maria! Maria!
I was worried you wouldn't be
here in time for the festival!
Huh? So there's a
festival today?
[MARTHA] Indeed. It's your
favorite one, no less.
We're pleased to have you with
us, lad and you, my dear Maria.
Welcome home.
This is home!
[ANN] The English returned
to their island,
and at long last, the endless
warring was over.
This was all many years ago now.
Sure as they call me Ann,
I can tell you Maria and Joseph
lived out a happy
life in our village.
Her name was Maria, the
same as the Blessed Mother,
and as Heaven and
Earth both knew.
Maria was a witch.