Do you have what
it takes to Buddyfight?
Choose your favorite world
and use special cards to summon
its powerful monsters
into reality.
Challenge other fighters
and Buddycall your toughest ally
to fight by your side.
Get ready to raise a flag!
♪
Why did you interfere?
Do you know how long
I've been waiting for
the chance to defeat Ryuenji
and reclaim my honor?
There was no guarantee
you would win.
It was a risk.
Enough mind games!
You know I was ready.
We've been training for weeks
in real world conditions
at Azi Dahaka's battle arena.
Battle Aura Circle!
Rouga!
♪
No, Cerberus!
This is not over!
‐Not yet.
‐I thought you were destroyed.
(roars)
You evolved; I didn't
think that was possible.
Armorknight Cerberus Ace!
(roars)
Demonic equip combination
with Demonic Spirit
Swirling Darkness!
Roaring Charge!
♪
We're stronger than
when we first fought him.
If that's true,
then what satisfaction
would you gain
from a rematch now?
What do you mean?
Don't you know?
Ryuenji's not in a position
to use the Future Force anymore.
Don't tell me
you were behind it!
Maybe I was,
maybe I wasn't.
♪
Thank you for bringing
the kids back safely.
No problem,
take care of yourselves.
Hey, Tasuku, what
happened back there, man?
Uh...
If there's anything
I can do to help,
just say the word!
Tasuku's been working
really hard lately.
He's probably just
a little tired.
Okay...
You ready?
Yeah.
(door opens)
Stay in school, kids.
(car starts)
♪
Boy, I wish I could have seen
Gao and the others fighting
against those students
from Sengoku Academy.
If you really wanna see,
Takosuke recorded it all.
Tako‐chu!
Thanks, I'd love to!
Me too, me too!
We can give you
the play‐by‐play!
I'm prepared to comment.
‐Can I help?
‐This guy's in.
‐Ditto, bro.
‐That'd be great.
Maybe I can learn
something, hey, Z?
You watch it if you want;
it's not like I'm dying
to see myself lose
so Gao can swoop in
and save the day again.
Hey, that smell!
You mean your stinky feet?
(sniffs)
Mm!
Grandma's cooking, oh,
that off‐the‐chain human food.
Let's eat.
Tako‐chu!
I think he's hungry, too.
Actually, I'm quite peckish.
That's weird, I smell perfume.
Huh?
(giggling)
What do you think of it, Gao?
To show my appreciation for all
you accomplished at Sengoku,
I've arranged for a surprise.
Ta‐da!
(all gasping)
I've had some of the tastiest
ingredients from all over
the world flown in on
my daddy's private jet,
and Gao's grandma agreed
to cook up all your favorites.
It's the last I could do
after you defeated
those barbarians from Sen‐Cad.
Did you think of me
when you were away
in the mysterious
mountains, Gao?
Huh, listen to me
when I'm talking to you!
Hey, thanks, Suzuha,
this is awesome!
Uh...
What?!
The Skyhome is where?
Lying in pieces somewhere
in the Chohakone Mountains.
Sorry about that.
It was an accident, honest.
Don't worry about it.
My lady, what are you saying?
‐You're not mad.
‐Even a little?
No, it's really not
a big deal, you guys.
The Skyhome is just
one of the many places
I own around the world.
(relieved laughter)
Take a seat, the show's
about to start!
Prepare yourselves
for highlights of
the exciting action
from Aibo's recent
Buddyfight Challenge
against the notorious
Sengoku Academy!
Tako‐chu!
First, some backstory;
things all started
when yours truly witnessed
former Aibo student
Rouga Aragami swoop down
and take our friend
Kiri Hyoryu
away against his will!
What?
But it wasn't against my will.
Are you serious?
Paruko had us
worried over nothing?
(grunting)
Whoa, so you're saying
I missed the Demons Who Think
They Can Dance
marathon for nothing?
(nervous tittering)
No biggie, come on,
let's watch the video.
I equip Demonic Spear
Swirling Darkness!
In the first match,
Tets tried to pull off
a one‐turn win against Rouga.
Would it be too harsh
to say that it was
an epic fail?
Yo, what's the dealio, A‐dawg?
Why'd you gotta be calling me
out in front of my peeps
all the time?
I cast Solomon Shield!
You're a fool!
I cast, your spells disappear!
Let me introduce
Fang Dragon Declaration!
But I was having so much fun!
Swirling Darkness
penetrates Beleth.
(explosion)
The second fight
was even crazier.
The Dragon Lord's immense power
cannot be underestimated.
Only the brave dare
to challenge him.
Genma was there, too?
Boy, I would have loved
to see him fight in person.
Well, lucky for us,
he was just hanging around
when our blimp crashed.
Genma battled one of
the four demon generals,
the most powerful
fighters of Sengoku.
This guy was
a little different, bro.
He was a Legend World fighter.
We found out that Genma
already met him when he
was training in the mountains.
♪
Kemura was this
totally hyped frog,
but it wasn't cool
when he used
the Hate Card Dragon
Vanquishing Sword Ballmung
to defeat Genma.
Isn't that like a counterbalance
that targets a certain opponent?
They're not against the rules,
but they're not
honorable either.
♪
Allow me to review
the third fight
starring the lovely Kazane.
In the beginning,
Kemura seemed
to be making up
for using a Hate Card
by trying to lose,
but he soon listened
to reason and changed his tune.
I call to center King
of Forest, Zlatorog.
(screaming)
And, in the end,
he fought valiantly.
Huh?
What makes you think
you know anything
about my Kemura anyway?
(screams)
The way someone
fights says a lot.
♪
And my big brother
was in the fourth fight!
Equip!
Five Heavenly Swords Onimaru!
There was a grudge
between him
and his opponent, Kanahebi,
that I didn't even know about.
He never tells me
his secrets anymore.
There really wasn't
that big a deal, Akatsuki.
but he was a real kind
of heavy style ninja.
An heir to an organization
our dad tried to put away.
The sweet smell of victory,
Cherry Blossom Storm!
Huh?
(gasping)
(grunting)
♪
Five Heavenly Swords Onimaru,
Twisted Spirit Purification!
That's nothing, I'll give you
the deets on the best match yet.
I was wondering when I'd get
to see Gao in action.
Raremaro Tefudanokimi,
a Four Demon General.
He used Legend World Two, but
Gao had a big surprise for him.
You used Magic World?
How'd you do that?
It's all thanks to Drum's
training in other worlds.
I got to used one of my awesome
new decks called Magic Guts!
One of your decks?
Gao‐wow was really
amazing out there.
You should have
seen him, so inspiring.
I had something to do
with it, too, you know?
Mega Blast!
(incoherent screaming)
This is gonna hurt!
That was his first time
using a Magic World deck?
After that one, there was
a majorly scary battle.
His strength was incredible.
The last of the
Four Demon Generals,
his name was Shosetsu.
He's a Legend World user
and his Buddy's
Immortal Sword Durandal.
He has an item for a Buddy?
That's right.
Immortal Sword Durandal!
For the first time ever,
I was actually afraid
of Buddyfighting.
(grunting)
Morgan le Fay!
No!
♪
Nin, nin!
Shiden!
♪
You've fallen
right into my trap!
Shooting Star!
(bloodcurdling scream)
♪
It didn't break; it's true.
It was one of my
worst‐ever defeats.
(screaming)
Amazing, I can't believe
how strong he is!
Yeah, and he was trying
to become even stronger.
Check it!
It was really intense,
and that time, I was using
another new deck called
Tempest Thunderknights.
Gao, are you actually flying?
I know, right?
Drum finally gave me
his awesome Buddyskill!
You're not so tough.
Man!
Check it out,
he really loses it!
What's happening?
There's no way that
I should be losing.
I'm supposed to
be proving myself.
It's time, Dark Core,
give me all you have.
‐I want unlimited power!
‐Is that what I think it is?
Do as I say, I order you!
Huh?
Immortal Sword Durandal,
Divine Protection Prydwen.
Hey, you can't equip
two items at once!
I know, but he kinda trumps
that rule when he made
the power of his cards real.
(grunting)
Enough of this!
(grunts)
(hysterical caterwauling)
I could use a hug!
It wasn't supposed
to go down like this!
Oh, did Tasuku make the power
of his cards real, too?
Sure did!
Look at him,
isn't he dreamy?
He even looks good
with his hair long!
I don't know, but thanks
to him, I got a do‐over
with the real Shosetsu.
I call to the right,
Thunder Knights
Drum Bunker Dragon!
Crash Drill Ram Bunker!
And then, it was down
to just me and Rouga
for one final battle
to win it all.
What?
A Dungeon World deck, too?
How many do you have?
This is the last one.
But it's super awesome, man!
And, get this,
it's called Brave Soleil!
Paper!
Come on, Rouga!
I don't want to!
It was sweet,
even Rouga kinda seemed
like he was loving it out there.
Just know when
all's said and done,
I'll be the victor here.
♪
What do you want me to do,
it's the only monster
that I have left.
I can't wait to take
a bite out of you!
Come on, open your present!
Demon Break Slash!
♪
Who'da thunk this could happen?
(grunting)
Both of them are
at zero life points!
I destroyed Brave
Equipment Glory Seeker!
I almost forgot about that!
You're kidding!
Is an ability like
that even possible?
Check it out!
I got Cecelia's Spell Disarm.
Game over.
Winner: Gao Mikado.
Huh.
That's how Gao won
the challenge for Aibo
and put those ruffian
Sengoku students
in the loser's circle
where they belong!
So, what did you
think there, hey, Kiri?
It reminded me of something
I wanted to ask you, Gao.
What is it?
I was wondering,
would you Buddyfight with me?
Sure, but why me, exactly?
After watching you
at Sen‐Cad, I need to know
how I measure up against you.
I get it.
Meet me in a dojo
and we'll have a match.
I have an idea, Gao‐wow.
Why not use your brand
new deck that has me in it?
I guess.
That okay with you, Kiri,
if I use Magic Guts?
Why not?
Gao's still pretty
new to Magic World,
so I should counter with
the Danger World deck
I built at Sen‐Cad.
It might just be
enough to beat him.
♪
Kiri Hyoryu, wasn't it?
And why didn't you bring
him to me like I asked?
(growls)
Don't tell me you thought
that having him closer
to Gao Mikado would
be better for him.
You really believe I would
think something like that?
I wouldn't be surprised.
Huh?
"Don't interfere;
I will train him."
That's what you said, isn't it?
I don't remember
asking you to train him,
did I, Rouga?
(grunts)
I see you're up
to your old tricks,
hey, Aragami?
Causing problems
for Master Kyoya
with your selfish ways.
What a warm welcome.
Careful, your face
might stay like that.
Sophia, how are you?
Don't I do a great
student council
president impersonation?
Kyoya!
♪
Well, well, Azi Dahaka.
I thought you might
be interested in witnessing
a rare spectacle.
Hey, that's Mikado.
Is he about
to fight against Kiri?
Armorknight Ogre to the right
and Armorknight Minotaur
to the left position!
♪
Hey, so where's Asmodai?
He had some errands to run, yo.
Armorknight Ogre,
go attack the fighter!
(grunts)
Minotaur, now it's your turn!
I cast my Solomon's Shield!
Gao nullified Minotaur's attack!
Wow, what a move!
I pay two gauge
and use two life points
to cast Fang Dragon Declaration!
(grunts)
He broke through
Solomon's Shield
like it was nothing!
Now, get ready for
my boulder‐piercing spear!
(grunts)
End of move.
All right, nice one!
♪
He got Mikado down
to three life points
on his first turn.
What beautiful technique,
and his attack's flawless.
You must introduce him to me,
the Great Elf Kabala.
I pay one gauge and call
to the center, Qinus Axia!
Now, this might sting a little.
Great Thundershock!
(grunts)
Well, Gao‐wow, aren't you
glad you listened to me?
Awesome, I call to the left,
Magician of Glass,
Will Glassart!
And after that, I call Mana
Booster, Melerqim to the right!
Will Glassart, attack Kiri!
I cast Battle Aura Circle!
Once again, our up‐and‐comer
uses a spell
to nullify Gao's attack!
Wow, when did Kiri
get so amazing with
his Danger World skills?
Yeah, he's killing it, bro.
I attack Kiri with Melerqim.
(grunts)
Can I really go again?
All yours, Axia.
What's this?
Mikado's using
a Magic World deck?
This kid really is too much.
Tell me, is there anything
that he can't do?
Terumi Kuchinawa, right?
Yeah, maybe,
and who might you be?
One of the toughest
Buddyfighters around!
Hey, that's enough, now.
As you wish, sir!
Uh.
I'm gonna send Armorknight Ogre
to the Drop Zone and Buddycall
Armorknight Asmodai
to the right area!
Did he say Armorknight Asmodai?
Oh yeah, a Demon Lord
in Danger World!
Oh yeah, oh yeah!
What did you wanna talk about?
Could you please transform
into a Danger World monster
for me today?
Hang on, is that even, like,
a thing you can do, A‐Dawg?
Course I can, I am
a demon lord, aren't I?
But I'm surprised
you knew about it.
I read it in one of
the training manuals
at Sengoku.
Think fast!
(whooshing)
Oh, man!
When called to the battlefield,
I instantly destroy
the opponent's left
and right monsters.
All right, Armor Knight Asmodai,
attack Axia!
I'm on it.
Oh, just when Gao‐wow
finally started using me.
I cast Magical Goodbye!
(grunting)
No problem, I'll just send
Minotaur to attack you.
Moo.
No chance, I cast Quick Summon
and Axia to the center!
Here's a wake‐up call.
Great Thundershock!
(grunting)
Axia's attack and defense
get a big boost from
Quick Summons' ability.
I'm talkin' 2,000 points.
That's not enough, Gao‐wow.
Minotaur has 5,000 attack!
Even with my bonus,
I only have 4,000 defense.
I got it all covered.
I'll just use another Magical
Goodbye to keep you safe.
(grunts)
I never expected Gao to be
so good with Magic World.
But I've got this.
Not bad, but try to block
my Boulder‐Piercing Spear!
(crash)
This match is really heating up.
You know, they kinda remind me
of myself a few years ago.
Will I get get
a chance to fight 'em?
All right, you won't
be sorry, Kyoya.
I promise.
♪
I call Axia to the center!
Me again, little one!
Great Thundershock!
(grunting)
Okay, I'm gonna pay one
gauge and Buddycall
Drago Wizard Magician Drum
to the right position!
Aw, yeah!
Love the outfit!
Come on, Drum, attack Kiri!
Get a taste of my Drill Blaster!
♪
(coughing)
Axia, finish this!
With pleasure.
♪
Game over.
Winner: Gao Mikado.
I lost, even with
Asmodai's power.
I knew I wouldn't be
good enough to beat him.
Oh, yeah, this one's
for my little sis.
Yeah, it was!
That's what I call
an awesome fight.
My man's got some
mad skillz, yo!
(whoosh)
Drum, I have great news!
I made a decision!
Wait, Kiri!
What do you mean,
you're leaving?
Oh, Drum!
Are you saying
you miss me already?
Nuh‐uh!
Where'd you say you're going?
Being around you two lately
has helped me realize something,
the truth, if you must know.
(whoosh)
Is that I want to bond
like you two have,
so I'm setting off
to find my own Buddy.
Just like that, we're free
of the cuddle dragon.
Knowing him, I'm sure
he'll find a great Buddy.
♪
Be honest, Kiri, do you really
think your playing style
is suited for Danger World?
What's that?
Ever thought about
switching things up?
I mean, its natural
that you wanna win
with the first world
that you chose.
I'm not saying to stop using
Danger World, but it might
be a good idea to try out
different worlds and see
how they fit,
just like he's doing.
I think you're gonna be a little
lonely now that Axia's gone.
Stop, someone'll hear you!
It just means
more pudding for me.
Then why are you freaking out?
♪
Oh, good, you came.
Take a seat, Gremlin.
Well, now that everyone's here.
You are all unique talents
who have been specially chosen
to use my disaster force,
and you are, in a matter
of speaking, my friends.
(chuckles)
Yeah, sure, you say that.
You're a really good player.
Wanna be my friend?
♪
Join me, let's change the world.
Pledge yourself to disaster.
To be clear, we'll be adding
those two we just saw
to our ranks?
They could be useful.
Not just two.
(chuckles)
There's a third
that I have my eye on.
♪
It's time for‐‐
Tasuku and Gao's
Card of the Day!
Today's card right here,
Armorknight Asmodai.
I never knew Asmodai
could turn into a card
from another world!
Yeah, but you have
to sacrifice another monster
to call him,
but once he's called,
he has a powerful ability
that destroys the opponent's
left and right monsters.
I guess you could say
that as a Danger World monster,
his ability's
even more dangerous.
So, what do you think, guys?
Think you can
open up one of these?
You'll never know
until you try!
♪
Next time, a mysterious
criminal fighter captures
some of our friends,
and you'll never guess
what he wants for a reward!
Next episode...
Join us for a Buddyfight!