Do you have what it
takes to Buddyfight?
Choose your favorite world
and use special cards
to summon its powerful
monsters into reality.
Challenge other
fighters and Buddy Call
your toughest ally
to fight by your side.
Get ready to raise the flag!
Counter final!
I cast!
♪
Let the world distort.
Turn back the sands of time and
erase all sadness from the past.
Sword of Nothingness,
Distortion...
Punisher!
(rumbling)
♪
The live coverage of the
Gaen Cup has resumed, sir.
Put it on the main screen.
You must believe how
shocked I am to discover
his true identity,
we couldn't have known
that the Purgatory Knight
was Tasuku Ryuenji.
Yes, yes, of course, we would
never have hidden the truth.
I can only speculate
why he wished to hide
his identity from all of us.
Perhaps for some reason
he wanted to compete
in my tournament as an unknown.
But did you see it?
That counter final card he used.
It's a perfect example
of the new cards
that will soon be available
as the world's most
incredible game
continues to improve and evolve.
(clapping)
(applause)
(cheering)
I was afraid that
this might happen.
Still, it's hard to believe
he'd take such drastic measures.
It seems Team Purgatory
is actually Team Disaster,
meaning that Tasuku‐‐
Has become a member of Disaster?
‐You really think so?
‐It is possible.
Well, well, what
do we have here?
Looks like you're wasting
valuable work time gossiping.
‐No, Commander, we were just‐‐
‐Uh‐uh‐uh.
Back to work, you two.
We were discussing
Tasuku Ryuenji.
I see, who would've
guessed he'd enter
the Gaen Cup under
an assumed name?
The scandal, this means
he has no intention
of returning to us.
I guess it's probably
for the best.
I'm glad we cut him
loose when we did.
(laughing and groaning)
♪
There can be no doubt,
Kyoya Gaen is the one
behind Nobari and his cronies.
We now know the
face of our enemy.
I agree, time for phase two.
Hm.
(panting)
Wait, you're really
gonna talk to Tasuku?
I have got to get
to the bottom of this.
I gotta know what he's thinking.
Welcome back to the
Gaen Cup semifinal
between Team Destiny
and Team Purgatory.
And if you haven't heard,
we had a surprising
appearance by Tasuku Ryuenji.
Even with his frosty cool new
look he's still super dreamy.
Now get ready, 'cause the second
fight of the match will feature
Team Purgatory's Rouga Aragami
and his Buddy, Cerberus Ace.
Opposing him from Team
Destiny is Jin Magatsu
and his Buddy, Evil
in Heart, Yamigitsune.
It's a rare
canine‐monster showdown.
Ruff‐ruff‐ro!
It's true, they're both
canines, but a little fox
is no match for
a ferocious wolf.
You're all talk.
My fox here will have
you running in circles.
I've wanted to fight you,
Magatsu, since I was at Aibo.
I just hope that your
nickname, The Uncrowned King,
doesn't prove a
disappointment to me.
I guess I should be flattered,
but guys like you are why
I avoided events like
this in the first place.
By agreeing to have
Buddyfights with show‐offs,
‐I risk damaging my reputation.
‐What do you mean?
I mean, if I was foolish enough
to beat you, I'd lose my title.
Are you suggesting that you
could beat me if you wanted to?
What if I am, there's only one
way to find out, isn't there?
♪
(laughing)
Whoa, whoa, whoa,
whoa, what's going on?
Did I just hear those
two laughing together?
Are they forming some sort of
bond no one will understand?
Kind of like my
bond with Tasuku.
The power of the Ace
will destroy you!
Dark Luminize,
Ace Defeat!
A terrifying spectacle's
about to begin.
Luminize,
Crazy Phantom Carnival.
Buddy...
fight!
‐Time to raise the flag.
I'm with Danger World.
I fight for Katana World.
Tasuku, open up!
What can I do for you?
You are aware this is not
your team's waiting room.
Drop the act, Ice Queen, we
have business with Tasuku.
Gleipnir.
‐Ahh!
‐Stop it!
Disaster Force has the
ability to make the power
of the cards into reality.
You're tempted
by it, aren't you?
You won't brainwash me like
you did all the others.
Oh, really?
Like you did with
Kiri and Shosetsu,
and then you used your
power to manipulate Tasuku
when he was feeling low.
For some reason, everyone
loses it when they get
that Dark Core Deck
Case in their hands.
You Disaster guys keep
saying that you're trying
to save the world,
but how do you think
hurting people is
gonna do that, huh?
‐You're a joke!
‐Sofia.
Please free Drum
from those chains.
You are here.
Ahhh, that hurt!
Let's go, you can't stay
here with these guys.
Actually, Gao, you're
the one who should leave.
Understand I'm not being
manipulated by anyone here.
I chose Disaster.
I joined of my own free will.
‐That's not true!
‐It is true.
I lost a Buddyfight to Kyoya
and it opened my eyes.
‐You wouldn't get it.
‐Tasuku!
Rouga has the first move.
Charge and Draw.
Vanquish all with
everlasting strength.
I equip Explosive Axe,
Ricdeau Demon Slay!
I caught your fight
against Shosetsu.
I know the restrictions tied
to equipping that item.
You can't call a monster
to your center position.
Gotta say, it takes guts
to leave yourself open.
I'd never do that.
So you're not a
big risk taker, huh?
Well, I'll show you
what it really means
to live on the edge.
I cast set spell,
Final Battle Skill,
MAJI Demon Slay.
♪
He just blocked
your center area.
This'll be fun.
That wiped the smile
off your face.
As long as this set spell's
engaged, we will not be able
to call size two monsters
or smaller to the center.
Brace yourself, here he comes!
(shouting)
♪
End of move.
That's a new one,
this set spell forces
both players to leave
their center wide open.
I guess now Jin has no
choice but to match Rouga's
no nonsense fighting style.
Poor Jin, his Skull Warrior deck
is just not built for that.
It was crafted to slowly
cause damage to his opponents
with monsters than can return
after being destroyed.
Show's over, yo,
sounds like Jin‐Boy's
on the express train outta here.
What do you think there, Zanya?
And draw.
Charge and Draw.
You think you've got
me at a disadvantage.
I know something you don't.
Now sit back and watch.
I call Tempest, Garo‐oh
to the right position.
And to the left,
Treachery, Jakikarasu.
I activate Garo‐oh's ability.
By paying one gauge, his power
increases by 3,000.
He also gets the ability
to do a double attack.
No pun intended, but
I'm more than equipped
to punish you with
some frontal attacks.
Now, Garo‐oh, go say
hello to the fighter.
(shouting)
Garo Slash!
One more time!
Feel the burn!
Treachery, Jakikarasu, why not
play him your favorite tune?
♪
‐White Noise!
‐End of move.
How is Rouga still standing
after that triple attack?
Look at that smile, he actually
seems to be enjoying this.
As Garo‐oh can only stay
on the field for one turn,
he's now eliminated.
Oh well, what can you do?
Your move.
I thought you'd at least
have the courage to equip
an item and attack me directly.
And put all my cards
on the table?
Your wit will be your downfall.
I Buddy Call Armorknight,
Cerberus Ace to the right.
Rouga gains one life
point with a Buddy Gift.
Sic him, Ace.
(whooshing noise)
♪
Demonic equip combination.
Cerberus Ace
has entered the soul
of Explosive Axe,
Ricdeau Demon Slay.
He put Ace into the card's soul
and increased the
item's critical by two.
I call Armorknight
Minotaur to the right,
and Armorknight Ogre
to the left.
Rouga shows he means
business setting up
his triple threat
fighting formation.
Copy cat, it's just
like the Gao formation.
So then, Minotaur has a critical
of three, and Ogre's is two.
Explosive Axe, Ricdeau Demon
Slay normally has a critical
of three, but in this case,
with Ace in its soul
it gets increased to five.
That's a total critical
of ten and one attack.
It's just like Rouga to set
up such an awesome move.
He can't lose this now.
Say your goodbyes, Your Majesty.
No one can defend
against ten critical.
Hold on just a minute.
Even if I can't call a
monster to the center,
I can still move Jakikarasu
over to protect me instead.
Don't waste my time!
Ogre, clear that pretender
out of the center.
Ogre!
(explosive noises)
That was easy, now I cast
Demon Way, Geppakugiri.
He did it, when an opponent
defeats one of your monsters
the effect of that counter
spell takes out one of theirs
at the same time, way to go.
I always say, they aren't
destroyed for nothing.
Looks like you're wide open.
There's nothing standing
between us to protect you now.
Ricdeau Demon Slay!
I cast.
‐Huh?
‐Art of Body Replacement.
No matter how powerful
your attack is,
it's useless if it doesn't
hit your opponent.
I don't believe what I'm seeing!
Jin's Art of Body Replacement
completely nullifies
his opponent's attack!
Who would've guessed that
he could survive an attack
of 10 damage without
even a single scratch!
Not bad, kid.
Good to see you finally
giving everything you've got
to win a fight, but why now?
What made you decide to
start taking it seriously?
I realized I was wrong.
To be honest, you could even say
that I finally saw the light.
What're you talking about?
Like you, I fell into
a world of darkness.
For the longest time, I didn't
think I could trust people.
Sadly, the only thing I found
I could believe in was money.
For you, that thing
has always been power.
You crave it, so much in fact,
that you've descended
into darkness for it.
You don't know me.
I know you're like anyone
else living in darkness.
You long to see the
sun again, like I did.
That's what inspired
me to try harder.
‐That sun is Mikado?
‐Don't make me say it,
it's embarrassing,
but you're right.
He's the one who helped me
rise out of the darkness.
You're saying that for you,
the sun is your friend?
‐Then it'll be the same for me.
‐Huh?
♪
In honor of my friend,
I, Rouga Aragami
promise you this, I will
not lose this battle.
I told you about the day that
I decided to protect people,
when I thought it was
the duty bestowed upon me.
And then the Future Force
awakened within me.
But it‐‐I didn't know that
it would never be enough.
♪
Game over, winner, Kyoya Gaen.
I just lost.
I can't believe
Kyoya defeated me.
You say that the Disaster
Force and the Future Force
are the same thing,
but I just won.
So tell me, can you tell
the difference between them?
♪
You're in a rush to grow up
because you want
to protect people.
Take it from me,
you're way off base.
You're chasing
after an illusion.
What do you mean?
A lot of adults these days
only think about themselves.
You know it as well as I do.
Just look at the
criminal fighters who use
their Buddy's powers
to commit crimes.
Or the high‐ranking members
of the Buddy Police
who swore to maintain
law and protect us,
but have now become corrupted.
Do you really think that you can
achieve any sense of justice
by joining forces with them?
In the end, you're
not being protected.
All they're doing is using you.
Are you saying that
I've been nothing
but a pawn this whole time?
Trust me, the society that
we live in today won't last,
but the new generation
can change the future.
So please, join me.
We both know that
this is what you need.
Use this Dark Core to
show those crooked adults
your sense of justice.
We can be friends if you accept,
and together we'll
save the world.
Together?
To save the world.
♪
That's why you left
the Buddy Police?
You think that joining
Disaster is the answer?
And tell me, just what
are you planning to do
with that Dark Core
Deck Case anyway?
He'll use it to
increase our numbers
and help recreate the world.
That's enough talk for now.
You have a decision to make.
Will you accept this
Dark Core or won't you?
‐Tell me now.
‐I don't know, I...
Stay true to yourself,
Gao, it's who you are.
Yeah.
We have no choice but
to respect your decision,
but first, I'll need
to erase your memory
‐of this conversation.
‐No, don't!
‐Dragonic Shoot!
‐Nice try.
Breathen Gard!
‐Leave him alone!
‐Grim Reaper.
‐Kiri?
‐Is that the Disaster Force?
Not quite, but be
prepared for anything.
‐Why do this?
‐Jackknife Dragon!
(flames whooshing)
It's Jack!
Kiri, do you wanna tell
us what's going on?
I can't really explain it.
Even though I gave
up the Dark Core,
I can still make the
power of the cards real.
Now listen, Tasuku, I know it
won't mean much coming from me,
but Jack has something
he needs to say to you.
Don't bother, I know what
he's gonna say already.
Please don't.
Tasuku, you said a bond
like ours was unbreakable.
♪
It is, you'll always be the most
important thing in my life.
Then why'd you go off
and become Buddies
with that wack‐job
Demios Sword guy?
Is that how you treat
people in your family?
I guess us dragons have a
different sense of loyalty.
Hm.
It's not true, not at all.
Life's great when I'm with you.
You make me feel like I belong,
but that's not a luxury
I can afford, not if
I want to do my duty.
I'm the one who has
to protect people.
So in order to bring
happiness to others,
I have to put aside
my own happiness.
That Dark Core is
rotting your brain!
The truth is, as long
as I'm protected by you,
I can't become stronger.
I hope you understand.
Even though you're
my best friend,
you're my greatest weakness.
What're you saying?
This is the new card that
I've picked out for you.
‐What do you think?
‐Demios Sword Dragon.
He's unique in that he can gain
strength simply by destroying
one of his comrades
in the field.
Gaining strength by
destroying an ally.
‐I've done it before.
‐No, wait!
If you use that card,
you know what'll happen!
I'm sorry, forgive me.
Tasuku!
♪
A human and a dragon unite!
Behold Jackknife Gold Ritter!
If I must,
I'll discard the one
thing I cherish most.
I know now it's the only way.
Congratulations,
that wasn't so hard,
and as your reward,
you get to be my friend.
No thanks.
I don't want any
friends or family.
I wanna be all on my own.
I've made up my mind,
not get outta here or else!
(explosions)
Ragnarok!
(wind howling)
Gao, get up.
Huh?
Hope you had a nice
nap there, kid,
'cause we got a
lot of work to do.
Drum's right, I'll tell
you what I just told him.
There's a reason that Noboru,
Jin, and Kazane teamed up
for this Gaen Cup tournament.
They're working together
to reveal the full extent
of Disaster's powers
and influence,
and to learn as much as they
can about Disaster's plans.
♪
I suppose you could say
that they're undercover.
But why are they doing it?
‐It's all for you.
‐You sure about that?
You've only got two cards
left in your hand,
but I know there's an
ace up your sleeve.
So let's see it already.
I cast Lord Aura Meditation.
Final phase.
He increased his gauge so
that he could use his impact.
I change Demon Slay's vow into
a blade and release it now!
I cast Ultimate Battle Skill.
Mega Demon Slay!
(screaming)
Oh no, Jin!
♪
Game over, winner,
Rouga Aragami.
An impact that uses
four gauge to cause
four damage to an opponent?
Even I wasn't expecting
a move like that.
Rouga ends the game with
an impressive impact,
which means Team
Purgatory sweeps
the best‐out‐of‐three match,
making them the first team
to move on to the
finals, booyah!
Everything is going according
to Master Kyoya's plan.
(crowd cheering)
Thanks for the show, Rouga.
Your skills are impressive.
I just hope Gao was
watching, for his sake.
Well played, Jin.
I wish you better
luck next time.
But you know I have to do what's
necessary to win the Gaen Cup,
because I made a sworn
promise to a friend.
♪
Everyone on Team Destiny
has fought against you, Gao,
and it's made them realize
what's important to them.
You shone with the warmth
of the sun on their hearts.
That's why they're doing this,
why they've chosen to help you.
♪
I really need a favor.
Anything for you.
Hear me out.
I want to get my family back,
and I'll need to fight
alongside you to do it.
Are you saying that you actually
wanna become part of my deck?
I am.
♪
Awesome, we're lucky
to have you, my friend.
You won't regret
this, I promise.
♪
‐It's time for‐‐
‐Tasuku and Gao's‐‐
‐Card of the day!
Today we're gonna tell you
about Treachery, Jakikarasu,
a new fighting force
for the Skull Warriors.
With 4,000 power, a critical
of 2, and the move ability,
this card's best for equipping
an item or fighting back.
'Cause it's size one,
you can revive it
with Return to the Underworld.
Every Skull Warrior's
deck can use one.
No matter how many times you
defeat it, it keeps coming back!
So what do you think, guys?
You think you can
open up one of these?
You'll never know until you try!
♪
Now that Purgatory Knight's
identity's been revealed,
Gao, Zanya and Baku
find themselves at odds
with each other,
so Tetsuya saves the day!
Next episode, Balle
du Soleil Collapses!
Join us for a Buddyfight!