♪
Get ready for
a cool new card game
that connects to
a parallel universe.
Special cards
act as portals,
bringing monsters to Earth
to become buddies with humans,
and through
friendship and courage,
help them take on
fight challenges.
It's called Buddyfight.
The sun's power
is limitless.
Its presence lights the way
for all living things.
A leader is a ray of
hope in the darkness,
like the sun itself.
You fade in comparison.
A true leader has the ability
to help others see their paths.
How do you expect to lead when
you're still figuring yours out?
You can't show people the truth
if you yourself are blind!
This truth is also like the sun.
You can shut it out for a while,
but with time it will
make itself known.
No one can stop it
from returning!
Brother!
Just think of the
Greek legend of Icarus.
Overconfident, he dared to
challenge the sun's power
and recklessly flew
too close to it.
Like him, you will be
brought down to earth!
Your time has come!
Eternal Spartand!
Attack the fighter!
(groaning)
♪
(shouting)
Stop it, you can't do that!
He still has one
life point remaining.
Finish him off.
(shouting)
Game over.
Winner: Genma Todoroki.
(sobbing)
No, it's not fair!
♪
(groaning)
(sniffling)
Nin.
♪
For the safety of both
players and spectators,
we must prepare the stadium.
What a silly question.
I mean, the Amanosuzu
reputation is at stake here.
We have the best
in the business
working around the clock
to make sure everything
will be ready for
tomorrow's big showdown.
It'll be as good
as new, guaranteed.
‐Huh?
‐That's right,
the ABC Cup
Championship Match is...
uh, should we actually
even call it that?
Anyway, the battle to
determine the strongest fighter
will be held tomorrow at noon.
I know I'll see you all there!
Man, I gotta wait till tomorrow?
It's cool, bro,
it gives us time.
They said we could
change up our deck...
if you want.
I don't know, let me think.
‐(doorbell ringing)
‐Huh?
Gao, Kuguru and Kiri are here.
Hey, come on in!
So, tell us, how's Zanya?
Aside from a bruised ego,
his injuries were minor.
He should be back at
school sometime today.
But it's good you didn't come.
He doesn't want
to speak to anybody.
I wouldn't either.
The guy did get his butt
handed to him out there.
(doorbell ringing)
Gao, Asmodai and
Tetsuya are here.
Okay, we're in here, people!
♪
(laughing)
Come on, have some, Tets.
This stuff tastes like winning!
Yeah, dog.
How about seconds, yo?
Sorry, guys, I don't
think we have enough.
Yeah, and who said
you could eat my dinner?
(doorbell ringing)
Gao‐‐
Mom, I don't care,
just let people in!
Nice room.
Oh, hey, it's that Do guy.
It's Doai.
Gao, I bring
a message from the chief.
Hmm.
Honey, I'm home.
(gasping)
Hi, dear, how was your day?
Are these all Gao's friends?
Yeah.
You do know that this is all
because of his Buddyfighting.
Huh?
Well, I figure that's the reason
he's been having friends over
to the house so often lately.
Oh.
(phone ringing)
Hello, Mikado residence.
Yes, this is Suzumi;
who's calling, please?
Huh?
Withdraw from the fight, Gao.
Genma told me to tell you that.
No, out of the question!
Them's fightin' words,
oddly‐dressed human.
Since he returned,
you've seen for yourself
how powerful our leader is.
You have no chance against him.
Our leader this,
our leader that.
Don't listen to him.
So, are you planning
on fighting anyway?
Yes.
That's exactly what
I thought you'd say.
I always do what I'm told.
If Genma orders me
to relay a message,
then I have no choice
but to obey him,
even though I knew that you were
gonna turn down his request.
Yeah, I hear ya.
Before I go, I want
you to know something.
Our leader's worried
about you and your safety
during the match.
That must be why he went
all‐out against Zanya,
to show us how
powerful he really is.
He probably wanted
to psych us out.
Then no one would blame Gao
if he decided to back down.
As a member of the Seifukai,
of course I want our
team to be victorious,
but to be honest,
I really hope you do well, too.
Your friends here did
save my life, after all.
Oh, stop it!
I don't remember
you doing anything.
To prove my appreciation,
I'll give you a little heads up.
Even with Duel Sieger,
you still haven't
seen the full power
of the Koryukien deck.
Huh?
♪
Yeah, right.
He's just trying to
mess with your head.
So what did they say?
You know, the same
old thing again.
They're persistent.
I get emails about it
practically every day,
like, "When will
Suzumi be coming?
We really need her
here in the U. S."
(sighs)
I agree, the students there
do need a better teacher.
Those videos you
posted of Gao training
get thousands of hits a day.
Everyone's trying to learn
the Mikado‐style Aiki‐jujutsu.
But, without
experienced instructors
to properly coach them,
everyone loses.
You know, they do
have a point, Suzumi.
They need help;
you should go.
You're the best
person for the job.
You have to do this.
No, I‐‐I don't think
I can leave them.
Listen, Hana's in grade three.
She can practically
look after herself.
Besides, Grandma's
living with us.
But still, I'd miss them.
We'd miss you.
♪
I found some great resources...
(overlapping chatter)
Wait, I called dibs!
Sorry, turtle butt.
Give me that!
Stop it.
Always fighting, you two.
Look, Grandma's made some more.
(humming)
Grandma, you rock!
I can't dish the dirt
before your match,
but Doai's right
about the Koryukien.
I guess we'll find out tomorrow.
There's nothing we can do
now but give it our best.
Why bother,
I mean, you can't win,
so why waste your time?
Genma's a Buddyfight machine.
Don't look now, but the
princess just walked in.
I came to tell Gao how
the construction is going,
and the next thing I know,
his grandmother has
me trying new things.
Well, if you don't want them...
Hey, back off,
I never said that.
It's like a party in my mouth.
Please, Mrs. Mikado,
let us help.
Why don't you come
hang out for a bit?
Aren't you tired after
making all that food?
You're right, thank you, kids.
Hmm.
I'm just glad she's quiet.
(gasping)
Hey, what gives, man?
Why are you adding bananas
to my grandma's recipe?
'Cause they so fresh, yo.
Trust us, we rock at mixing.
Toss in some of that
super spicy demon curry
‐while you're at it, Tets.
‐Have you lost it?
That's gonna taste
totally gross!
Now get out of the kitchen
before I get majorly agro!
Don't worry about Gao, Mom.
He'll be just fine.
Do you remember that
Mighty Sun Fighter uniform
that I made for you?
Well now it's the
perfect size for Gao.
I've even caught him
sleeping in it.
Guess it was a matter of time.
Kids grow up quick.
I miss you so much,
my dear sweet Yota.
(sobbing)
I promised myself I wouldn't
cry like this anymore.
I know you're with us in spirit.
I'm okay.
(sniffling)
I've been so scared
that someday Gao and Hana
would end up like you.
Maybe it's crazy,
but I thought that...
if I kept them close to
me for as long as I could
that they'd be safe.
That's why I force
Gao to train with me
every day and always
worry about where he is.
Oh, pretty silly, huh?
But, today I realized something.
Gao's got his own path now,
and it's turned out
surprisingly different
from yours, Yota.
And Hana's, too.
I guess it's about time
I finally give him this,
isn't it?
Gao, get over here
on the double!
Sorry, dear.
Here, take this.
Where did this come from, Mom?
I found it mixed in
with some of Yota's things.
Hmm?
I have no clue why
he had just one card,
but what I do know is this:
Yota kept it with
him all the time.
I never knew about it.
He would've wanted
you to have it.
Yeah?
And I think you should use it.
That would've made
him very happy.
Thanks.
Baku, Kuguru,
you'll never guess!
Check it out!
Do you know if Buddyfighting
exists in the U. S.?
Of course!
It's gotten to be
popular all over the world.
Then maybe I'll give it a try.
Are you sure?
A Sun Fist,
Sunshine Impact card.
Doesn't ring a bell,
must be outdated.
This one, it's rare.
But couldn't it throw off
your entire deck balance?
It belonged to my brother.
It'll be like
fighting alongside him.
♪
It's all good, bro.
Adding one card's no biggie.
It for sure won't mess
up your deck's balance,
especially not the mean
deck I've got goin'.
Thanks a lot, Baku.
But we are gonna need
a practice round,
so you'll need an opponent.
How about it, you guys?
‐Any takers?
‐I'll step up to the plate.
Pick this guy.
If you want a real challenge,
I'll do it, but you'll owe me.
I'll do it, I'm by far the
most superior fighter here.
Okay, I'll take you
all on at once!
Welcome back, everybody.
Feast your eyes on the
absurdly‐fast repairs
the Amanosuzu Company has made.
They've transformed
the fighting stage
back to its former
glory in just one day!
(laughing)
Paruko, you've
forgotten to mention
the other incredible feature
that we've added to the stage.
(crowd murmuring)
(exclaiming)
♪
We will now begin
the Aibo Buddy Cup
Championship Match, a. k. a.,
the Aibo Buddy Cup Extra Battle
to Find the Strongest Fighter
For Real Now Final Match.
First up is
Team Balle du Soleil.
They've made it all the way
from the elementary
school preliminaries.
The fighter is Gao Mikado.
Their opponent
needs no introduction
as the reigning
champions from last year,
Team Seifukai
and Genma Todoroki.
(cheering)
♪ At the core of our school
is a great hall to be sure ♪
I want to remix this, yo.
Yeah, I feel
a freestyle comin' on.
♪ We'll keep our eyes open
and push forward on our climb ♪
I guess my warning
didn't reach you.
I can't believe Doai was unable
to persuade a little junior.
Don't blame any
of this on Doai.
I'd never back down from
a fight, no matter what.
Overconfidence won't serve you.
We'll see.
Ancient Dragons,
awaken and bring your
fury to this world.
Bring fire and unleash
storms of rage!
Luminize, Koryukien!
Showering the sky with
scorching sun rockets!
Luminize, Soleil Dragon Deck!
Say it one more time
for me, folks.
Buddyfight!
(cheering)
Time to raise the flag!
I fight for Ancient World.
I'm with Dragon World!
(roaring)
♪
Gao will go first.
Charge and draw!
Come on!
I call Extreme Sword Dragon
to the center position.
♪
(grunting)
Full force attack on Genma!
End of move.
What?
Gao's turn is over already?
The player who goes first
can only attack once.
Oh, right, I forgot.
Draw!
Charge and draw, come on!
(shouting emphatically)
Casting Divine Dragon Creation
lowers our life points to five.
Storm Dragon Emperor,
Thundertornado
and Evil Crusher,
Steel Dragon Barrage!
have been drawn.
Rise & Fall of Dragons
takes our gauge to seven.
No matter who he fights,
Genma never takes it
easy on an opponent.
Watch this: I cast...
Dragon Emperor Legend
with one life point regained.
I charge and draw one gauge.
I get one life back.
Buddy Call to the center.
Uh‐oh, here it comes.
I'm ready.
(grunting)
Martial Arts
Dragon Emperor, Duel Sieger!
Whoa!
He's back!
It's Genma's legendary
buddy monster, Duel Sieger!
♪
Not only does he
regain one life point,
but if he has
a Dragon Lord in his hand,
he can place it in
Duel Sieger's soul
for a Soulguard.
This is gonna be more
fun than I thought.
Sieger, go show
"extreme" what that means!
Sieger Tornado!
♪
Now give Gao a taste of that!
Sieger Tornado!
(groaning)
End of move.
Hey, that's not fair,
he attacked him twice!
You're embarrassing me!
Draw!
Charge and draw!
Go, Gao, you attack
him twice, too!
Calm down, Mommy.
I equip Steel Fist,
Dragoknuckle.
I'm gonna call
Thunder Knight, Halberd Dragon
to the left position and
together will link attack.
♪
(grunting)
Hmm.
Welcome to the party!
Gao's defeated Duel Sieger
with a fancy link attack!
But it's quickly
resurrected with Soulguard,
and he still has
one soul remaining.
End of move.
That's one tough dude.
I know.
It'll make defeating
him that much sweeter.
You're weird.
Your move.
Draw!
Charge and draw, let's go!
(screaming)
Sending Fortune Dragon,
Forbolka to the drop zone
and adding two gauge.
So he's increasing the
gauge count even more.
He must be impressed
with Mr. Mikado
if he's resorting to
these kinds of tactics.
Halberd, move to
the center area.
I knew it.
I will protect you.
Sieger,
go and educate Halberd Dragon!
Sieger Tornado!
I cast Dragoenergy!
(roaring)
Counter attack!
You can try that,
but it won't beat his Soulguard.
♪
Final phase cast.
Even after surviving
two Sieger attacks,
Gao's gotta deal with this?
Evil Crusher,
Steel Dragon Barrage!
(groaning)
End of move.
Is he okay?
Talk about
a perfectly timed attack.
His skills and deck
are off the hook.
So, Gao, I hear you've
been calling yourself
the Mighty Sun Fighter.
That's ridiculous.
There can only be one champion,
and it isn't gonna be you.
You should've just withdrawn
when you had the chance.
Are you gonna take that?
Sounds to me like
we're getting to him.
He knows the
fight's not over yet.
We'll see if the Seifukai
can really take down
a strong team like ours,
or if Genma's all talk.
Hmm.
Buckle up, it's
about to get real.
Draw!
♪
Charge and draw!
I call Double Sword Dragon
to the left, and I Buddy Call.
All right!
Drum, to the right!
With Buddy Gift, I'll
recover one life point,
and I'll link attack
with Drum and Double Sword.
Let's do it!
♪
(grunting)
We did it!
I think you've forgotten
how resilient Sieger is.
Destroying him just
makes him more powerful.
What are you waiting
for, bring him out.
Call!
The Dragon Lord
Martial Arts Dragon Emperor,
Duel Sieger "Spartand"!
♪
(yelping)
(roaring)
♪
Okay, now what?
How do we fight that thing?
We've got this.
If we use Dragoknuckle,
our power will increase
by 2,000 for each gauge.
Even Spartand, with
a defense of 8,000,
can't handle Dragoknuckle
with a power of 8,000.
Steel Fist!
Freeze Shot activate.
(groaning)
Well, I'll be‐‐
Genma just discarded
Ice Dragon Emperor,
Glacies from his hand,
and by using one life point,
he was able to
nullify Gao's attack.
How brilliant!
Your move.
Draw!
Charge and draw, you're done!
(screaming)
Casting Dragon Emperor Legend
with five life
and with one gauge,
Dragon Outlaw is drawn.
So Spartand will be
attacking twice.
Watch out, Gao.
Eternal Spartand!
Attack the fighter!
I cast Dragonic Formation,
and Double Sword
moves to center.
♪
(grunting)
Then we'll destroy him!
Attack Double Sword
and then Gao!
Cast again!
(grumbling)
Blue Dragon Shield!
End of move.
Amazing!
Gao guarded himself perfectly
against two attacks by Spartand!
Oh, no, his first draw
is Thousand Rapier Dragon.
That's not good, bro.
Charge and draw!
This time he got
a Dragonic Grimoire.
Okay, we still have a chance.
♪
He actually pulled
Green Dragon Shield,
White Dragon Shield,
and Ironchain Dragon.
Yes!
What was that, Ironchain Dragon?
I call to the left
Ironchain Dragon!
♪
Somebody need a leash?
Using two gauge, I want you to
restrain Sieger with your chain.
That guy?
It'll take a lot of chain.
You can get more.
Rhystic Chain!
♪
By paying one gauge,
his chain can reduce the defense
of an opposing monster by 3,000!
But it only lasts
until the end of the turn.
That means Spartand only
has a defense of 2,000.
What's really cool is that
if Ironchain's defeated,
his effect remains.
Awesome!
Now keep going
and attack Spartand.
Ironically, this mammoth
could be defeated
by a Size 1 monster
with only 3,000 power.
Won't happen.
Cast Dragon Outlaw!
(grunting)
♪
And right cross!
(grunting)
♪
But it'll just come back
to life with the Soulguard!
Come on, Drum, you're up!
It's about time, too.
(shouting)
Crashing through!
You wish that I'd backed out.
♪
Hello there, I'm Paruko
here to guide you through
the world of Buddyfight.
We finally caught a glimpse
of the amazing
Duel Sieger "Spartand."
This enhanced buddy monster
can be called from the hand
after Duel Sieger
has been defeated.
Its power, defense, and critical
are off the charts,
so when you throw
in its Soulguard
and it's double
attacking ability,
how can Gao possibly
defeat a monster like that?
Can you open a buddy rare card?
What do you think?
♪
What's the real story
behind Yota's Mighty
Sun Fighter comics?
And will Gao finally be able
to show Genma who's boss?
Next episode:
The Powerful Sun Fist!
It'll be enlightening!