♪
Get ready for a
cool new card game
that connects to
a parallel universe.
Special cards
act as portals,
bringing
monsters to Earth
to become
buddies with humans.
And through
friendship and courage,
help them take on
fight challenges.
It's called
Buddyfight.
Thirsty for life!
(explosions)
Yeah!
Game over,
winner Noboru Kodo.
That wasn't luck,
it was strategy.
♪
It came to me while
I was trying to fit
the Vlad Dracula
card into my deck.
Hey, Noboru!
Hmm?
Nice match!
Save some for me, huh?
Oh, I will.
You can bet on it.
But you know what I'm
really looking forward to?
There is something
different about him.
Defeating both you
and Zanya on his stage
so I can win
the ABC Cup.
Hmm, keep on dreamin', man.
♪
(crashing)
I can't believe
this is happening!
Me, losing to
that grade sixer!
How is this even possible?
Then maybe you should
have just let Genma compete
instead of locking him up.
I don't know what
you're talking about.
Locking up?
Who's Genma?
Oh, yes, him‐‐what do
I have against that guy?
And you should know me
better than that.
I'd never resort
to such crude tactics.
‐Sophia.
‐Done.
♪
(laughing)
What a weirdo.
This is an outrage!
Keeping us down here
and taking our
deck on top of it.
It's embarrassing that I
could be tricked so easily.
Just wait till I get my hands
on that pain in the neck!
I'll tear him apart.
I'm getting us
out of here now.
Aaaah!
Huh, huh,
huh, huh, huh!
Stop, I've already tried.
I'm afraid
there's no way out
of this stone prison
from the inside.
I don't know why Shido
wants us down here,
but we're trapped
until he lets us out.
(water running)
Could be a long wait,
so save your strength,
you're gonna need it.
Okay, fine then.
(roar)
Dragons Duel!
Journey of the Tiger!
A‐ha, I thought it
was you, kitten shirt!
Mmm?
Seriously,
for the last time.
This happens to be
a tiger, not a kitten.
Whatever, I know
the difference.
And you're not
supposed to be using
your cell phone at school.
Shows what you know.
We're allowed to used them
during the ABC Cup Tournament.
Ah!
Cool phone case,
can I see it,
‐let me see it!
‐No chance.
Get away, what's
with you, anyways?
I didn't even
think you liked me.
Huh, why
wouldn't I like you?
Gao is always saying
nice things about you.
"Noboru's an awesome guy,
he's super cool,"
and stuff like that.
So why are you always
giving me such a hard time
and calling me kitten shirt?
'Cause you keep
saying bad things
about my brother
and his Buddyfighting.
Uh, girls
are so complicated.
Do me a favor,
just stop hanging
around me, all right?
Fine, I prefer lions anyway!
Huh!
It wouldn't hurt to let
me see it just for a sec.
He doesn't
mean it, you know.
Huh?
Are you sure about this?
Yeah, I think so.
We decided before
the school year started.
You know the
championship match
is two days away, right?
Yeah, but I
never even expected
to make it this far.
Still, there's so
much that remains
for you to do, my boy.
I know, it'll be okay.
Like you always say,
make a decision
and stick with it.
♪
But then we'd get totally
pummeled by Halberd Dragon,
wouldn't we?
So then maybe we should
equip an item card
or something.
Hey, guys, trying to
have a match over there?
‐Ah!
Who, us?
Just prepping for
the semi‐finals.
'Kay, if you say so.
A simulation,
what a good idea.
Kudos on your
dedication, bros.
You probably don't want us
spying on your plans
though, am I right?
♪
Hmm.
Yoink.
The thing is, I doubt
Noboru's gonna listen
to any of the ideas we have.
Sure he will, if he
knows what's good for him.
Otherwise, he's got
no chance against us.
Newsflash, guys.
Hmm?
Who are they?
What's going on?
How's it hangin'?
We're Noboru's
mom and dad.
Hi, everyone.
It's nice to meet you guys.
Noboru talks
about you a lot.
No offense, but
what are you doing here
in the middle
of a school day?
‐Noboru's leaving the country?
He's leaving on
a 6:00 flight?
Not tonight?
So he won't
be coming here anymore?
I don't understand,
why didn't he tell us?
I was afraid he might
not have said anything.
That's just like him.
It'll be weird
without him around.
Totally,
we should all chip in
and get him a
going away present.
Count me out.
What's with you?
He can't just ditch us!
That's so lame!
This could be the last
time we see this place.
Yeah, so what?
I don't really care
about that stuff.
The six years I spent here
weren't the greatest for me.
But at least‐‐
Nice match,
save some for me, huh.
I did make one good friend
I liked competing against.
Welcome to the first
semi‐final match
of the ABC Cup.
This is when the Buddyfight
action really heats up.
Both of today's teams
are from elementary school.
They beat the tough
middle school competition
to get here.
And each fighter
uses Dragon World
so you'll be glad you
showed up for this one.
What's with Gao?
He's totally creeping me
out with his rage face.
Now let's check out
the player interviews
we did before the
tournament started.
So, I'm Gao Mikado.
I'm in sixth grade and
I fight for Dragon World.
I want to shout out
to my team, Balle du Soleil.
Many of us also
affectionately know Gao
as the king of dumb luck.
Now let's meet his opponent,
the number two ranked
fighter in his grade,
Noboru Kodo!
I don't know, I guess
I went with Dragon World
'cause the
Dragon Knights rock.
Better than Armor Dragons.
Those guys are weak.
That was Team Rising Tiger.
Now let's get
this party started.
Hey, Noboru.
Huh?
Isn't there something
you forgot to tell me?
Thought you'd actually
get away with it, huh?
Huh, what's he
talking about?
I wonder what
I did this time?
I really can't ever catch
a break in this place.
Uh, who cares,
I'll play along.
I'm leaving anyway.
It'll be easier if
he stays mad at me.
With bravery and honor,
by order of the dragon,
the trusty sword
that reigns over villainy.
Time to luminize!
Knights unleashed!
Showering the sky
with scorching sun rockets,
luminize!
Select dragon deck.
How does the saying go,
when in doubt,
buddy...
Fight!
‐With pride, we raise the flag.
I fight for Dragon World.
And I fight for Dragon World.
♪
Gao will go first.
Noboru, just know that
I'll never forgive you, man.
Whatever, quit with the
yapping and start playing.
Come on, bring your worst.
I remember
when he transferred
to Aibo Academy
three years ago.
He always seemed to be alone.
Hey, Gao, that is your name,
isn't it, pal?
Why are you sitting
here by yourself?
It is recess, you know.
I'm just chilling.
Get real, come and play
some dodge ball with us.
We need a fourth.
Uh, for reals?
Well, I wouldn't
be asking if I wasn't.
Cool.
Back then, when I asked
him to join our game,
I didn't really
think anything of it.
Crash, Drill Ram Bunker!
End of loop.
That's what I call
an opening move.
Gao buddy calls
and challenges Noboru
with a direct attack.
Hey, you know that day
we first met each other
back in the third grade?
How can I forget?
You were sitting
all by yourself,
looking all sad and lonely.
I just had to
take pity on you.
I'm gonna buddy call.
Dragon Knight, El Quixote
to the right.
Here we go, Rocinante.
People used to avoid me,
and then one day you started
including me in things.
So why was that?
I felt sorry for you,
looking like a loner.
So I asked you to
play some dodge ball.
I call Red Baron
to the left.
In trust, I trust.
You have no idea
how stoked I was
that you let me
play with you guys.
Huh, whatevs.
We just needed an even
number of players is all.
I equip Twin Dragonblades,
Dragoanthem.
We would have asked
anyone to play,
it didn't have to be you.
I know that one.
He's using the Gao formation.
Guess you've got to
fight fire with fire.
Hey, stop copying my
big brother's moves!
Does she have a mute button?
I don't know, do you have
a fast forward button?
Uh, you guys, you're
harshing my mellow.
Quit embarrassing me,
all right?
Prepare for my attack.
You really don't get it.
Haaaa!
Aah!
Grrrr!
You won't get rid
of me that easy.
Oh, yeah.
But I wanted to fight.
Uh, that's not good.
An assault of glory.
Aaagh!
Taste the boom cake!
Uggh.
End of move.
Total bummer losing Drum
so early in the match.
Dragoanthem's double attack
is a wake up call for sure.
Yeah, his soul guard
was basically useless.
Well, that's a surprise.
I was expecting to see
different fighting styles.
It seems these two are a lot
more similar than I thought.
If it wasn't
for you that day,
I might never
had made any friends
or started Buddyfighting.
I draw.
♪
Charge and draw.
I call Thunder Knights,
Halberd Dragon
to the right.
And Thousand Rapier Dragon
to the left.
Come on!
♪
You've got a bad memory.
What about that
fifth grade gym class?
You showed me up,
so I blocked you out.
You mean that time
I kicked your butt in judo?
Is that why
you got all weird?
I equip Steel Fist,
Dragoknuckle.
♪
Yeah, that's how the
Gao formation's done!
How would you have felt?
You could have
taken it easier on me.
We all know you're this
big Aiki Jujitsu champ.
You didn't have to
make me look so lame
in front of everybody.
After that, people stopped
hanging out with you so much.
You can't tell me
you didn't notice.
What did you
want me to do?
Lose to you on purpose?
No, but you were
such a show off.
What were you trying
to prove anyway?
I move Red Baron
to the center!
Huh, urgh, Halberd Dragon,
go and destroy Red Baron!
Right.
Rahr!
I'm hit!
If you're so mad at me,
then why did you bother
to teach me Buddyfighting?
Because I thought
I could beat you.
It was supposed
to be payback
for making me
look bad in judo.
Thousand Rapier, attack
him together with me!
Hah!
Whatever your reason,
it's because
of Buddyfighting
that I was able to
make friends again.
By using Dragoknuckle,
Gao's gauge jumps up to three.
Noboru's down to
just four life points.
Let's see how he responds.
Your move.
Guess that was my bad then.
You're clueless,
but hang on.
You're about to be
severely enlightened.
It was like a bad dream.
I couldn't
believe that you,
a Buddyfighting newbie,
actually opened
a buddy rare card.
And then followed it up
by beating Tasuku Ryuenji
in front of the whole school!
You know how long
I'd wanted to do that?
I used to be number one
at whatever I tried.
But now it seems
like everyone's
getting better
than me at stuff.
It's not fair!
And it's not fun losing
to you all the time.
I've played this
game for longer.
Do you expect me
to just give up
and tell you I don't
have a chance against you
as a Buddyfighter?
No, but you sure
could have told me
a few other things, man.
It's real easy
for you to say.
You hardly ever
have to admit defeat.
I want to be the best.
I will be number one.
And I won't let
anyone get in my way.
You'll learn what
it's like to stand by
while the winner
gets the applause.
Then maybe you'll
understand what it feels like
to be me.
Let's see how you like this.
‐Stop!
Huh, huh?
What's going on, Noboru?
You're letting
his talk distract you.
Yeah, calm down.
Hey, what are you
guys doing in there?
You been here
the whole time?
We thought you
might need some help.
And I guess we were right.
That is what team
mates do, after all.
Right, team mate?
We were simulating tons of
game scenarios all morning
to prep for today's match.
We even did one for
the current situation.
No thanks, I can
handle it on my own.
It's under control.
Why don't you listen to some
friendly advice for a change?
Mmm, sorry, you're right.
Think of us as
knights in training.
What he said.
Fighting with
bravery and honor.
I never, well, thought
of you guys like that.
Well, I guess it's time
you started, huh?
Let's share
our feelings later
'cause now you gotta draw.
First I'll
analyze it for you.
Yeah, well I'm pretty sure
it's a little late for that.
You still have a
charge in draw, too.
Come on, just give it a shot.
Besides, we might
actually pull this off.
You don't know what
you're talking about.
We can't get
out of this one.
Let's try it anyway.
It's the knights code
to never ever give
up without a fight.
Draw.
♪
Hmm.
Green dragon shield.
So you're gonna charge
Dragon Knight, Masamune then?
Yeah, charge and draw!
‐Huh?
‐Nice one.
That's just the card
to help us get out of this!
You really think
it could help us win?
Abso‐freakin‐lutely.
You're a wicked
player, Noboru.
Drawing Slash
Strike, Dragoslasher
with the game on the
line is major league.
What's the hold up?
This plate armor isn't as
comfy as it looks, you know.
And it's not very noble
to keep an old man waiting.
Sorry, let's do this.
‐Go get him!
I'm gonna own this.
I call Dragon Knight,
Vlad Dracula to the left.
Here we go again.
Noboru's paid three gauge
to bring out that
powerful size two monster
that defeated
President Shido,
Dragon Knight,
Vlad Dracula!
I've arisen to quench my thirst.
Let us once again mark
our time together in battle,
young dragon warrior!
If you didn't know,
Vlad Dracula's
critical increases
with each Dragon Knight
that's in the drop zone.
Exactly how many are
there in the drop zone?
There are four.
Translation,
we're gonna kick it.
Vlad has four
critical points.
Good work, guys.
So let's see what
this guy can do.
Now I cast Slash
Strike, Dragoslasher!
Slash Strike,
Dragoslasher?
This isn't good.
That spell increases
his Dragoanthem attack.
To be more specific,
When there's a Dragon
Knight in the drop zone,
5,000 power can be
added to an item.
What?
That means Dragoanthem's
power is now 10,000.
And Noboru is able to defeat
any monster that's out there.
I move Halberd
to the center area.
♪
That's it, Gao,
you show him!
Show him what, kid?
That suped up Dragoanthem
is a major pain.
Doesn't look good.
Huh?
Hear me roar!
I cast Wrath of Dragon!
You shall not pass!
Say what?
The Wrath of Dragon spell
adds 6,000 power
and defense to an Armor Dragon
already on the field!
Which means Halberd Dragon
now has 12,000 defense,
so even Dragoanthem's
10,000 attack
can't defeat
Halberd Dragon now.
Not so fast!
Having said that,
Wrath of Dragon's
only effective
on the first attack
and not on the second.
Gotcha!
Arrgh!
Wow, Dragoanthem did
have a second attack!
Cool, this is so exciting!
I want Gao to win,
but I think Noboru
is super cool, too.
Hey, El Quixote,
go attack Gao again.
Right.
Let's ride, Rocinante!
An assault of forged
steel and courage!
Aargh!
Attack with Bloody Charge!
Noboru's in the zone.
Totally savage,
he can do anything.
People used to say that
about me all the time.
You're leaving
tonight, right?
Huh, sorry.
We heard you were
booking it out of town.
But no matter
where you go,
we'll always be
Team Rising Tiger,
won't we?
Yeah, of course.
End of move.
♪
They're right,
I can do anything
I put my mind to.
I can go anywhere and
I can become anything.
What a joke.
If he had just
one more Dragon Knight
in the drop zone,
he would have won.
Kitten shirt totally
dropped the ball out there.
Hey, it's not a kitten,
it's a tiger.
A super strong,
super awesome tiger!
Maybe you're right.
Whoa, really?
I think he might
have seen it, too.
That sun, I mean.
You're move.
Draw, huh!
Here we go.
Charge and draw.
Huh.
I can't help it,
I'm just so angry at you!
What's going on, pal?
What's up with you today?
It's because, you didn't
even give me any warning!
Uh.
I thought we were friends.
Starting final phase!
Huh, Gao, you don't know
what I think you know, do you?
After all we've been through,
you were just
gonna up and disappear
without saying anything?
You weren't even gonna give
me a chance to say goodbye!
Who does that?
I gotta say, man.
♪
That was a major burn!
I'm sorry!
♪
(explosion)
Game over,
winner, Gao Mikado.
And that's what
we call closure.
What a finish!
Team Balle du Soleil
sweeps up the first
ABC Cup semi‐final win.
Looks like they're on
their way to the finals.
And let's hear
it for the fantastic
tournament performance
from Team Rising Tiger!
Good luck, we'll miss you.
Ah.
(cheering)
This is exactly why I
didn't want to say anything.
Noboru, we have to board now.
Okay.
(phone buzzing)
Hmm?
Oh, a text.
Seriously, he never
gives up, does he?
Hi, Noboru, just
wanted to say I'm sorry
for always calling
you kitten shirt.
I actually
think you're great!
Ha, what, so the whole
family's texting me?
‐(phone buzzing)
‐Huh?
Hey, bud, we'll miss you.
Keep it real.
See you, Noboru.
You're really leaving?
More texts.
Maihama, Niitani, everyone.
Even Mr. Neginoyama?
Huh?
♪
It's Gao!
Uh.
Doesn't look like
they're gonna let you leave
without a big farewell, huh?
I hate these
kind of goodbyes.
You beat me, Gao,
you're a legend!
You're the best
player I've ever seen.
Win the cup!
♪
(engine soaring)
Hello there,
I'm Paruko,
here to guide you through
the world of Buddyfight.
As you know, the Buddy Card
office gives core deck cases
to each Buddyfighter.
But I bet you didn't
know the core gadget
can be changed to match the
characteristics of its owner.
They can be almost any
shape and size you want.
And during a Buddyfight when
your deck becomes luminized,
the core gadget
really goes to work
when it activates the
amazing buddy skill ability.
Can you open a
buddy rare card?
What do you think?
♪
Don't miss the countdown
to the second semi‐final
between Jin Magatsu
and Zanya Kisaragi.
With both fighters
from Katana World,
it'll be an epic showdown.
Next episode:
Mystique Explosion!
The Great Katana World Battle!
It'll be a blast!