Get ready for
a cool, new card game
that connects to
a parallel universe.
Special cards
act as portals
bringing monsters to earth
to become Buddies
with humans.
And through
friendship and courage,
help them take on
fight challenges.
It's called
"Buddyfight."
I pay three gauge to
activate Lethal Formation.
Secret Sword,
Shooting Star.
♪
(Shosetsu groans)
Did you see that?
He destroyed the item
using Secret Sword,
Shooting Star,
and gave him three damage.
Check it, yo,
Zanya's the man.
Forgot what I said, didn't you?
Maybe.
At the beginning of the fight,
I told you Durandal
never breaks, dents,
rusts, or shatters.
There's a reason why
it can't be destroyed.
It's an Immortal Sword.
♪
It didn't break.
It's true.
Durandal's as
powerful as they come.
(Zanya screams)
Zanya!
Game over.
Winner: Shosetsu Kirisame.
And there it is.
That should
wake Mikado up.
Maybe now he'll get
serious about his
fighting again.
Whoa, I never knew
fighting tactics
like this even existed.
I didn't believe
Rouga at first,
but if I study here,
I just might become
stronger like he says.
Maybe even as strong as Gao.
So, this is where
you've been hiding.
Uh?
Oh, Miss Vice President.
What are you doing here?
There's something I've
been meaning to give to you.
But isn't that‐‐
She's around here somewhere.
‐No!
‐Kiri!
♪
Here.
This is yours now.
(whimpers)
Why give it to me?
I don't want it.
This Core Deck holds
a special power.
If you use it, you'll
become very strong.
Isn't that what
you've always wanted?
Yeah, but not like this.
I heard what happened
to Doai when he was
forced to use one.
I just can't!
(shrieks)
(screams)
(grunts)
Huh?
Gao's mom has
got it goin' on.
Snap out of it, kid.
Get a hold of yourself!
A rare few contain the
core with this much power.
Huh?
Doai didn't have what the
Dark Core case requires.
You do.
You were always
meant to have it.
From what we've
seen of your skills,
we believe this
elusive power
may have found its master.
I really don't
know what to say.
I never thought
I was good at anything.
Now you're telling
me I'm special.
I'm so confused!
What should I do?
I'm confused, too.
Don't you want
to become strong?
Huh?
Just remember this:
The only thing of
any value in this world
is winning!
Caw, gotta win it!
The more I
think about it,
the more I realize
Rouga is right.
I've been listening
to Gao's advice
and I never win.
This is a chance
to prove myself.
♪
I'll do it.
And become
the strongest ever.
Where are we?
Sengoku Academy.
Really, Sengoku?
I've read about it.
Buddyfights are
really popular here.
Maybe even more
than they are
at Aibo Academy.
I know what
your hopes are.
You're no longer satisfied
having friendly
Buddyfights
with your pals, are you?
I don't know.
Tell me what it is
you desire the most.
Actually, I wanna be
like my friend, Gao.
Why are you so
fixated on Mikado?
He's really good
at thinking on his feet.
I mean, I don't think he's
ever lost a Buddyfight.
♪
After I've trained you,
you'll be able
to beat 100 Mikados.
So, forget about him.
(shouts)
Mr. Aragami.
Welcome back, sir.
Open the gate.
Right.
Sorry, sir.
Go on in.
What are you doing?
Your job is to refuse
entry to unknown individuals
and send away trespassers.
Huh?
Here at Sen Cad,
winning a Buddyfight
is the only way
to get what you want
out of someone.
If you wanna get past us,
you're gonna have
to beat both of us.
It shouldn't matter
who your opponent is.
Take the victory
and show me
what you're made of.
Your path to ultimate
victory starts here.
Okay.
I'll do my best.
There is no your best,
only the best.
Hmph!
I'm not gonna lose to them.
Not to anyone!
(screams)
♪
I'll finish you off
with Black Drake!
♪
Game over.
Winner: Kiri Hyoryu.
(exhales)
♪
Not bad.
But I won't go
down so easy.
Bring it on!
‐Raise the flag!
Who would start
a Buddyfight
this late at night
without asking me first?
Huh?
Figures that
Rouga is involved.
I call Fighting
Dragon, Demongodol!
Get that eagle!
(screeches)
Why me?
Huh?
(grunts)
Game over.
Winner: Kiri Hyoryu.
Hm.
Rouga, I actually won!
Can you believe it?
Hmph.
I think I'm ready
to prove myself.
Follow me, then.
♪
What do you make
of this, Durandal?
You can be sure,
Rouga's a wild card.
Why him?
Clearly, I am the best
person for the job.
♪
Where are we?
Let the books be your guide.
Uh.
♪
I do like to read.
Match records?
Study them closely.
Look for strategies.
These are records
of Buddyfights.
The cards are listed, too.
I get it, this is a special
Buddyfight classroom
or something, right?
Absorb all you can, protege.
Become stronger
than Mikado.
♪
I hear you
changed your mind.
You're ready to start
winning the big fights now,
aren't you?
If you use it,
everything will be
as you wish.
But be warned.
There is a risk involved.
But that's true
of most things
worth having.
♪
Kiri!
Huh?
Can you hear me?
Hey!
Hold on, we're coming!
I'm in here!
Where are you?
(struggling)
I almost had him.
Kiri, you in here?!
Aren't you the
Aibo vice president?
Ugh, you okay?
Come on!
What happened?
Hey, man, say something!
With Zanya's defeat,
Aibo finds itself
down to just one player.
And that player is none
other than Gao Mikado.
Can the ABC Cup
champ defeat Shosetsu
and tie things up?
Or will he be defeated
and end the contest
here today?
Come on, Gao, it's time
to take center stage!
Hm?
The Mighty Sun Fighter!
Paging Gao
to center stage!
Come on, already!
The whole school's
relying on you!
Sorry, lady,
he's not here.
Gao and Drum went
to the dorms to get
some lunch, and they
still haven't come back.
You're telling me our
champion's literally
out to lunch?
I keep trying his cell,
but he's not picking up.
I hope nothing's
happened to them.
I hope he has my order.
I feel your pain, yo.
You know you have
bananas, right?
You just ate
the last one!
They don't grow back
right away, you know?
(shouting)
Every which way
it's coming down.
Stop throwing things
onto the field!
Someone could get hurt!
‐(glass breaks)
‐Takosuke!
Hey, are you okay?
Vinegar?
If this keeps up,
my Buddy, Takosuke,
will be turned into
a giant pink pickle!
(shouting)
This is not
spectator etiquette!
Stop it, you guys!
And no more vinegar!
♪
He'll show.
It's in his
competitive nature.
Gao's not the kind
of guy who would
ever back down
or run from a fight.
We're gonna lose
this by default.
And if that happens,
we'll never find Kiri.
Oh, where can they be?
I knew I shouldn't
have let them go alone.
They're so hot‐headed.
Don't worry, we'll
go look for 'em.
What do you say?
It might be fun.
I'll follow your lead.
Buddy Skill on.
I can't let Magic World's
biggest celeb go hungry,
especially not one
who's my Buddy,
so better split,
know what I'm saying?
Triple time.
Thanks a mil, A‐Dawg.
Don't get beside yourself.
What did you do to him?
Hoo, I made it.
Don't move!
What are you
trying to pull here?
"Pull here"?
I'd be happy
to show you.
Dark Core,
activate Disaster Force.
♪
Huh?
Lesson one:
Stay out of my business.
♪
Are we flying?
No, I think we're falling.
How can we help Kiri
from way up here?
Beats me.
This is the
opposite of falling!
I'm so confused right now.
(screaming)
♪
Hey Drum,
your Buddy Skill!
What?
Come on!
This would be
the perfect time!
(nervous laugh)
About that...
What's this?
What are you doing here?
I told you not
to interfere.
Let me guess,
you also have
something to do
with Mikado's absence
from the match out there?
Tell me what you've
done with him!
About 7,000 meters up by now.
Huh?
You are aware he doesn't have
a Buddy Skill, aren't you?
Oops.
I'm really sorry, kid.
The truth is that...
I can't give you
my Buddy Skill
until I figure out
how to use it!
That's okay.
You can do it, man.
You really believe
that I can?
I'm sure of it, Drum!
You can do
anything you want.
You're right.
What am I afraid of?
I so got this,
just like I got stronger
by training in other worlds.
(groaning)
I think I can.
I think I can!
♪
Buddy Skill on.
A star in the daytime?
It looks like the light
from a Buddy Skill!
Check it out.
Wicked.
Now you're talking.
♪
This is awesome.
‐Yeah, right!
‐Hurry up, Gao!
Kazane.
What's wrong?
You can't miss your match.
You could lose
automatically.
On the double,
young man.
I think we're ready.
Yeah.
Aren't you forgetting
something, guys?
The food!
(shouting)
If Gao doesn't appear
by the count of 10,
he'll lose by default.
I'm sure no one
expected things
to go like this.
What could be keeping them?
I don't know.
What a bummer.
I can't believe
I lost my match.
Nin.
(groans)
Where are they?!
Shosetsu, look behind you.
Huh?
♪
When did she get here?
The real concern
is what she's holding.
♪
The core!
Would you like
to have this power?
♪
One!
Two!
Three!
Four!
Five!
Six!
Seven!
Eight!
Nine!
Ten!
Mind if I crash?
Let's get this party started.
Those two have
always lived
for the drama.
What a relief.
You had us worried, bro.
For real.
Yeah!
Gao just got
his groove back.
Word!
No big deal.
(munching)
Hey, is anybody hungry?
No, duh!
What have you got there?
(laughs)
Who's the best
demon ever?
No competition, A‐Dawg.
That feel better?
Takosuke,
Takosuke, Takosuke!
Then let's get back
to calling the match.
Takosuke!
Now that we finally
have both players here,
we can officially begin.
You don't think I know
what you're up to?
I understand
your frustrations,
but remember, Rouga,
you're not the one
calling the shots around here.
Neither of us are.
I will not tolerate
any more meddling from you.
I have my orders, got me?
Cracking the skies,
and rumbling the ground.
Luminize!
The forceful
Tempest Thunder Knights!
How many decks
is he packing?
Don't forget
Drum has trained
in three different worlds.
There was Dungeon World,
Magic World, and
of course Dragon World.
And we built three
completely new decks
focusing on the major
strengths of each world.
Now...
ready to win
this thing, Drum?
Yup!
A thousand swords
defeating the enemy
with a thousand vows.
Dark Luminize!
Fortress of Swords!
At long last, Buddyfight!
‐Time to raise the flag.
Dragon World!
Dark Buddy Skill on.
Legend World.
Gao is, once again,
back to his usual
Dragon World colors,
but he'll be
using a new deck.
And is it me or does
his Buddy look a little
different than usual?
Enough talk.
Shosetsu is up
for the first move.
♪
That's weird.
He has a different
vibe than before.
I call Great Magician,
Merlin to the center position.
Incubus' Blood.
Thanks to Merlin's ability,
two of the top five cards
in his deck have just
been added to his hand.
Come on, Merlin!
Do your magic.
Cloud of Doom!
(Gao struggles)
End of move.
This is unsettling.
Yeah, I've got
a bad feeling
all of a sudden.
Actually, I do too.
I know exactly
what you mean,
but for very different reasons.
I told you not to drink
that gallon of water.
I draw.
My Tempest Thunder
Knights deck is gonna
blow your mind.
Charge and draw.
Now I call...
Thunder Knight, Halberd
Dragon to the right.
And to the left,
the dangerous
Thunder Knights,
Broadsword Dragon.
Then I equip Thunder
Blade, Dragobreaker.
And I cast the set
spell Thunder Formation.
He's using a set spell?
That's unusual.
Gao's really
changing it up.
What's Thunder Formation?
If a Thunder Knight uses
its move ability during
the opponent's turn,
a card will be added
to Gao's gauge.
That's super awesome, yo.
♪
Like a bolt of lightning,
we will flash across
the battlefield in
a rage of flames.
♪
Never turning
away from danger,
we fight for our comrades
as they are a part of us.
For we are the
mighty Thunder Knights!
Let's do this, you guys.
Halberd, get Merlin!
Yes, sir.
Vile beast!
♪
Awesome, the center's open.
Come on, Broadsword.
Go ahead and
attack the fighter.
Right.
Prepare to be
put to the sword, no escape.
Ancient Thunder Clap!
And cue Dragobreaker!
I cast Holy Grail!
You're not so tough.
Oh, man.
End of move.
Shosetsu just blocked
Gao's big attack.
He's really stepping it up.
I call Knights of
the Round Table,
King Arthur to the right.
And Great Magician,
Merlin to the left.
Incubus' Blood.
Once again,
with Merlin's ability,
he adds cards
to his hand.
I Buddy Call and equip
Immortal Sword, Durandal.
Here it comes!
It never breaks, dents,
rusts, or shatters.
It's the fabled Demon
Sword of Legend World,
the Immortal Sword, Durandal.
And it can never
be destroyed.
Has our champion
finally met his match?
Halberd, move
to the center!
By using Thunder Formation,
that move adds one
card to Gao's gauge.
Heh.
What a waste of a move.
King Arthur, shall
we link attack Halberd?
I will protect you, sir.
Hiya!
Trusty sword,
time to penetrate.
(Halberd shouts)
Halberd!
Quell the uprising.
Ugh!
King Arthur's ability
gives one card
to Shosetsu's gauge.
Merlin, attack the fighter.
I cast Blue Dragon Shield!
Gao defends well,
blocking Merlin's attack.
And Blue Dragon's
ability puts another card
in Gao's gauge.
End of move.
(scoffs)
Your move.
Draw.
Charge and draw.
I think it's time.
Are you ready, Drum?
Never been more ready.
Let's beat this guy.
That's the plan!
All right.
Buddy Call...
Thunder Knight,
Drum Bunker Dragon
to the right!
(Drum shouts)
My Buddy's not only
a triple threat,
he's also three times
stronger than before.
That's right.
Thunder Knights,
Drum Bunker Dragon
is now on the scene,
and I'm ready to dance.
It's time for‐‐
Tasuku and Gao's‐‐
‐Card of the day!
Believe it or not,
we have our very own
Dungeon World cards.
And today's card
is one of them.
It's called Legendary
Brave, Tasuku.
When this card makes
a link attack with
an Adventurer Card,
both cards gain the
ability to penetrate.
Which means this card
deals equal critical damage
to your opponent.
That means that you can
do a penetrate attack
with two cards at once!
So, what do you think, guys?
Think you can open
up one of these?!
You'll never know
until you try.
♪
Next time, Gao's
Thunder Knights deck
backs Shosetsu
into a corner,
forcing the Legend
World fighter to call
on his Dark Core.
Next episode, "The
Legendary Sword Excalibur!"
Join us for a Buddyfight!