Do you have what it
takes to Buddyfight?
Choose your favorite world,
and use special cards
to summon its powerful
monsters into reality.
Challenge other fighters,
and Buddy Call your toughest
ally to fight by your side.
Get ready to raise the flag.
What now, kid?
I take away one
card from my hand,
and equip Brave
Equipment, Glory Seeker.
Look out, he's coming!
He's got spunk!
Okay, Drum, let's
link attack Gagnar!
Time for Rock‐Paper‐Scissors.
You wouldn't dare!
So you think you
can beat me, do you?
Really, don't make me laugh.
Rock, paper...
Scissors!
Scissors, for the win.
Engage Rock Ram Bunker!
Go get 'em, Drum!
♪
So, what do you think?
Is it possible?
The boy's even better than
we thought, leave him to me.
So it's all according to plan.
♪
What do you think you're doing?
When Sofia left,
I only promoted you
from Student Council
Secretary to Vice President
because you convinced me
that you could handle
the demands of the
work, Miss Kuchinawa.
Your opinion of
yourself is overblown.
I wouldn't even recommend
you for trash duty.
I'll show you,
I can do this job!
I hope so, I despise
training new people.
I don't have to take this.
Sorry, what was that?
I'll be right back.
The nerve of that guy.
He acts like he's the king
of the school or something.
So, what do you think of her?
You mean Terumi?
Yes.
Well, her school spirit
leaves something to be desired.
All right, give me an E!
For excruciating.
I think you should
just give her a chance.
The girl is simply beautiful.
Especially her devotion
to Master Kyoya.
It's unmatched by
anyone else in Disaster.
Sure it's the same girl?
Oh, brother, what are
you two fighting about now?
This sneaky thief ate
all of my yummy pudding
while I was in the shower!
Did not, scale face!
I think traveling
to all those other worlds
has messed up your lizard brain!
Oh yeah, well, at least I
have a brain to mess with!
(bickering)
You okay?
Yeah, I think so, let me just...
Maybe I can help.
Hey, Drum, lend me
your Buddy Skill.
I'm doing this for her.
Buddy Skill, on.
Let's take her to
the nurse's office.
Good call.
Hello?
Where is everybody;
Nurse lady?
Please, I'm fine,
don't worry about it.
No way, you're
looking kind of pale.
I think you should
rest for a while.
Yo, yo, yo, yo, yo, yo, yo, yo.
This again?
Yo, yo, yo, yo, yo, yo,
yo, yo, yo, yo, yo, yo.
Did you guys have
candy for breakfast?
We're practicing for a
superfly dance contest, yo.
Those guys, they're
always up to something.
♪
What I want are those three.
Tasuku Ryuenji,
Kiri Hyoryu,
and, of course, Gao Mikado.
What?
That Sun Fighter dumb‐dumb?
Why's he so special?
Terumi, I have a job that
requires your talents.
‐Who, me?
‐You are registered
at Aibo Academy, aren't you?
Yes, that's right.
Then what I have in mind for
you should be a piece of cake.
Isn't that too much
responsibility for her?
She'll do fine.
Well, I could be
doing more too.
I have talents.
Start by being supportive.
You want me to support her?
Do you have a problem with that?
No, not at all, just making
sure I heard you right.
Perhaps I should go to
this Aibo Academy as well.
It sounds like a lot of fun.
That okay?
Yeah, I think so.
Now, Dark Core,
activate Disaster Force.
♪
Mighty Elixir of Aesculapius.
With this, I can
make that silly Mikado
do practically anything I wish.
Check out our new rap.
Lay it on me.
♪ Mic check, mic
check, one two ♪
♪ Tets and A‐Dawg in the house ♪
♪ When I'm dancing to my jam,
everybody knows who I am ♪
♪ Just throw your
hands up in the air ♪
♪ And wave them
like a special rare ♪
♪ One, two, three,
four, five, six ♪
My head.
Huh?
Better already?
You're like a superhero.
Yeah, I'm fine.
Did you drop something
on the floor a second ago?
Drop something?
It wasn't me!
It must've been
noise from that music
your friends were singing to.
Thank you, come again.
You really didn't
have to do that.
Yes, I did.
Hang on, excuse my friend,
of course we'll eat them.
Hope you like them.
And with these, Gao Mikado
will be mine to control.
Are you ready, everybody?
Let's do it one more time.
♪ My rhymes are so delish,
I get As in English ♪
♪ Core Gadget says End Move, but
I'ma say right now let's grove ♪
♪ One, two, three,
four, five, six ♪
Not again, now my
headache's back.
♪
Oh, no, there goes my
Elixir of Aesculapius.
That was our best yet.
We so nailed it, yo.
You guys are killing it.
First place is gonna
be yours in no time.
You were great.
Kind of makes you want
to dance, doesn't it?
That sounded like
an encore to me.
Come on, now, let's freestyle.
‐No, please don't!
‐Huh?
♪
I can't explain it, but
their singing and dancing
is one of the most irritating
things I've ever heard.
Disaster Force, activate.
♪
They'll be sorry.
I'll get them for
messing up my chance.
Those dancing fools
are in for a treat.
What's up with her?
I'll never understand girls.
She possesses two qualities
that nobody can beat.
One is her devotion
to Master Kyoya.
And the other one?
Her heartlessness.
The reason she
wears those glasses
is to hide her true feelings.
But if you look deep
into her eyes,
you start to see how
cruel she truly is.
That girl?
You're kidding me.
Time to tear it up.
You know I will.
Shazam.
That was off the chain, homie.
Represent.
Hey, don't you have a big gig
down at the Dragon City
Music Stadium in a few?
Yeah, gotta pay the bills
and show my fans some love.
All right, that's my buddy, the
hippest dance show host around.
I just got a Buddy Choice
Award for "Most Chill Demon."
Of course, I am the only
demon in the category.
Well, catch you
later, I gotta fly.
Stay real.
Now what'll I do.
Maybe I'll cruise to Gao's
and feast on his Grandma's
super fresh cooking.
Huh?
That you, A‐Dawg?
Did you forget something again?
Huh?
What's your deal?
What's my deal?
You're always in my way!
Well, where you
trying to get to?
I summon Divine Armor, Aegis.
Huh?
Your dancing is so irritating.
I'm putting a stop
to it right now!
Hey, that's not paid off yet!
It doesn't make sense!
Tell me right now, why is it
that you annoy me so much?
Answer me, banana brain!
Well, maybe you just
like indie pop better?
I could tell you
what's going on.
That was fast.
Wrong day, homes.
Good thing you're
not my manager.
The gig isn't until tomorrow.
Huh?
But it's a good thing,
because it looks like you're
losing a fight to a girl.
It's not what it looks like!
Hey, how's it going?
I'm Asmodai, the demon.
You don't intimidate me.
Now, you said you could tell me
why you irritate me so much.
Go on, spit it out.
Tell me now!
It's like I'm being hypnotized
by your lack of
shame or something.
Trust me, it's just as easy as
one‐two‐three, little sister.
Tets is always keeping it real,
in other words, he's free.
The reason you're
so irritated by him
is because you're way too
focused on power and approval
all the time, which means
you can't be free like he is.
What are you saying?
I am free.
Wait, at least I think I am.
To use a different lingo,
you're what we demons call,
"All shriek and no freak."
That's why you're
jealous of him.
He didn't care what peeps think.
That's crazy, I'm not jealous.
Taking life seriously
is what made me powerful
in the first place.
This guy's always acting
a fool, because he's happy.
It's happiness, and not power,
that makes him strong.
That's ridiculous.
If you won't give me
a proper explanation,
then I'll fight you for it.
For starters, here's my buddy.
Now you're in trouble.
Meet Gorgon
Three Sisters, Medusa.
You guys think you're so tough?
You're about to learn what
true strength really is.
Gorgon Three Sisters, huh?
I've never seen one
up close before!
Why don't we go over
and talk to her, huh?
Whose side are you on?
I don't know, she doesn't
look all that strong to me.
She's half snake and half girl.
Spoke too soon!
She's breaking my heart, I guess
that part must be the girl!
I've been called many things,
but no one's ever
called me weak.
So much for your
silly theory, demon.
No way, just leave him alone.
Don't sweat it, there's
nothing she can do to me.
I don't know.
Why are you protecting
your monster, banana boy?
Comes natural, A‐Dawg ain't
just the flyest Buddy ever,
he's my main man.
You actually care about him?
See, that's what I've
been telling you, lady,
he's a strong human because
he surrounds himself with homies
who've got good vibes, and he
sticks by them in hard times.
I don't want to hear it!
If my medusa shoots her arrow,
it'll be lights out
for dancing boy, here.
Are you afraid of
attacking us directly?
What is that spear,
anyway, an accessory?
Go on, come at us.
I promise we won't move at all.
You gotta recognize that
using a dark power like yours
doesn't mean that you're
any tougher than those of us
who don't use it.
Time to face facts,
if you hang around people
who sweat the small stuff
and you let them
tell you what to do,
then you're always
going to be thrown off
by guys like us who know
how to keep it real.
How's this?
If you manage to beat
Tets in a Buddyfight,
then my boy here will
do anything you say.
Say what now?
What you mean "anything"?
You really think
that he can defeat me?
I'll take that as
a yes, let's roll!
Bring it on.
You don't stand a
chance, banana boy.
Release the evil eye,
scatter curses everywhere!
Dark luminize, Gorgon Empire!
♪ C'mon, feel the beat ♪
♪ Dance of demons,
it's time to defeat ♪
Let's luminize it, yo!
Ticka ticka ticka, yo!
Time to raise the flag.
I fight for Legend World.
And this guy's with Magic World.
Let's go, it's time to
prove your true strength.
We all in believe in you.
And the 72 Pillars of Solomon
will follow your lead.
Prepare yourselves!
Charge and draw.
I call Divine Stallion, Pegasus!
♪
End of move.
That's just the beginning.
If I were you,
I would give up now.
You don't know him,
he'll never give up.
Yeah, now it's our
turn to crank it up.
Dig it, I draw,
charge and draw.
I call to the center,
Street Racer, Eligos.
Don't believe I'm steely,
just wait until I pop a wheelie.
I call to the left, Zepar.
I Buddy Call to the right,
Demon Lord, Asmodai!
♪
(screaming)
Showtime!
I discard a card from my hand.
Now take it away, A‐Dawg.
Sorry, big fella!
Pegasus!
Time for some
Dangerous Backdrop!
That does it.
Eligos, Asmodai, Zepar,
synchronize your routine.
Woohoo!
Mind if I drop kick?
Top Side Blaster!
♪
End of move.
Your move.
I won't let you
get away with that.
Draw, charge and draw!
I call to center, Gorgon
Three Sisters, Stheno,
and I'll pay one gauge and call
Gorgon Three Sisters, Euryale
to the left position.
♪
Whoa, check it, she's calling
the whole Three Sister Family!
Stheno, the oldest of
the Gorgon Three Sisters
is supposed to have
the chillest vibe ever.
The other sister is Euryale.
She's a tough warrior, but
I've heard she's really cool.
And the third sister, Medusa,
she's as powerful as they come.
Okay, Stheno, attack
that creep Eligos!
♪
I'm gonna use one life point,
and return Eligos
to my hand, yo.
I didn't know he
had that ability.
Then, Euryale, attack
banana boy, right now!
(grunting)
Follow it up with
a double attack!
I'm gonna cast Solomon's Shield.
Go!
End of move.
Okay, time for
our counterattack.
Oh, really, I've got
Stheno in my center position.
With a defense of 6,000,
she can't be destroyed
with a single attack.
And since you can't reduce my
life points with a link attack,
I'm pretty sure you're stuck.
Magic world's got
lower power, it's true,
but don't ever
underestimate what we can do!
He's right.
To make up for our low attack,
we've got big spells
in our magic sack.
Let's razzle and
dazzle them, Tets.
Okay, I cast.
And I'm gonna flip the script
by using one life and paying
four gauge for Great Spell,
Devil's Rock and Roll.
He returned Stheno
and Euryale to my hand?
Hold up, my turn's not over.
I take the top five cards
in my deck, and pow!
Out come as many super
awesome monsters as I want.
♪
Thought you'd seen
the last of this guy,
but rock and roll
will never die.
Yeah!
♪
Here comes the best part!
Leave some for me!
I cast Power of Mythology!
♪
She makes it look easy.
That's the Power of Mythology.
It has the ability to nullify
an attack but just once.
Oh, no!
Your move.
Now it's my turn
to pay you back!
Draw, haha!
Charge and draw!
Watch out, I cast
Elixir of Aesculapius!
With it, I can control both
gauge and life however I want!
I don't believe it,
her gauge and life
points went up one each!
I choose to buddy call
Gorgon Three Sisters, Medusa.
And once again, I'll pay one
gauge to call to the left
Gorgon Three Sisters, Euryale.
♪
And now, I'm going to discard
Gorgon Three Sisters, Stheno
from my hand.
♪
What happened?
Did she really just
defeat all of them?
Didn't you know?
When Medusa's on the field,
and I discard a Gorgon
card from my hand,
all monsters in
my opponent's area
that are size one or
smaller are destroyed.
How is that even possible?
Medusa, go attack the fighter!
♪
With Euryale's double attack,
I've basically won
this fight already.
You better think again.
I'll use one life and call to
the center Street Racer, Eligos!
Three times lucky,
I'm gonna ride the wind.
How is he able to call
a monster during my turn?
Didn't you know, Eligos can be
called during my opponent's go.
Well, it won't help.
I cast Power of Mythology!
I don't get it, though, what is
she using a spell card for now?
I pay two gauge and give the
ability Penetrate to Euryale!
That's a different
ability than last time!
Depending on what I need it for,
the Power of Mythology
has three abilities.
The one I just
used is a spell
that can give the ability
Penetrate to one of my monsters.
♪
I am the strongest!
Game over.
Winner, Terumi Kuchinawa.
So pathetic.
Your skills are impressive.
Help me understand,
I'm confused why
someone as good as you
would live your life
following someone else's orders.
Your Buddyfight with
Tetsuya was fun, wasn't it?
It's because you got
to do your own thing
and really be in the moment.
So why don't you throw
away that dark power
and let yourself be free?
I couldn't do that,
I like the way I am now.
♪
The power you possess
can make a difference.
Change things for the better.
So what do you say?
Do we have an agreement?
If you join me, we can
save this world together.
♪
You mean that everything I've
strived for is within my grasp?
You don't know what's best
for me, leave me alone!
‐But I‐‐
‐So what's it gonna be?
What do you want me to do?
The deal was, if you won, I'd
do whatever you wanted, right?
But singing and dancing are
pretty much my only skills, yo.
One last time, hit it,
wicka wicka, what?
♪ It's okay that she
loves being gloomy ♪
♪ I think my new
friend's gonna be Terumi ♪
(beatboxing)
Please, stop it!
Say what?
Never again.
Sorry, I didn't
catch that last thing.
Don't come anywhere
near me ever again!
You got me?
Hm.
♪
Really?
So little Terumi messed up, huh?
I know, the poor little dear.
Maybe now Kyoya will put me
in charge of the next one.
And how is he
supposed to do that?
You know you don't
even go to this school.
No problem, I've already
taken care of the details.
♪
Now's my chance.
I'll get that kid he wants.
I'm Davide Yamazaki.
♪
It's time for...
Tasuku and Gao's...
Card of the day!
Today's card is special.
Fighting Dragon Emperor,
Demongodol Ark.
His abilities are counterattack,
Soulguard, and he can
even destroy weapon cards.
And after calling him by putting
him on a Duel Dragon,
your opponent won't be able
to attack any other card.
Put him on top of Fighting
Dragon Demongodol and call him,
he'll be way strong
with a three Soulguard.
So what do you think, guys?
You think you can
open up one of these?
You'll never know until you try!
♪
Next time, Kiri
is sad to find out
he'll be transferring schools.
To make sure no one forgets him,
he challenges Kazane
to a big final showdown.
Next episode, Fenrir of Fate.
Join us for a Buddyfight!