♪
Get ready for a
cool new card game
that connects to a
parallel universe.
Special cards act as portals
bringing monsters to Earth
to become buddies with humans,
And through
friendship and courage
help them take on
fight challenges.
It's called Buddyfight.
What's the matter, Gao?
Are you okay?
Have you seen Rouga?
Um, actually he's
left school for good.
Why don't you become his friend
and try explaining it to him?
You're right.
But it's too late for that now.
Nothing is ever too late,
believe me.
When you get to
be as old as I am
you learn it's our mistakes
that shape us into who we are.
I guess.
Then for me,
this has taught me to try
and become friends
with everyone.
♪
Welcome to Earth, Sir.
Are you interested in
doing some sightseeing?
Sightseeing?
What do you take me for?
I don't have time to engage
in such trivial nonsense.
A knight's intellect
seeks nobler pursuits.
Sorry.
There's certainly
many other things to do
during your stay.
(panting)
(barks)
But I want popcorn!
Okay, but leave them for dinner.
Wait!
Heel, (indistinct)
The real reason I came
to this world is...
I'll just check off sightseeing.
Deck building to victory!
A‐B‐C.
Aibo Buddy Cup?
Is it that time of year again?
What exactly is the
Aibo Buddy Cup anyway?
You really don't know?
How could he?
Don't forget, Baku.
He wasn't even Buddyfighting
the last time that it was held.
Yeah, but I figured he
would have at least heard of it.
The Aibo Buddy Cup,
also known as the
ABC Cup for short,
is a major Buddyfight tournament
open to both the elementary
and middle school
students at our school.
It's the number one event for
those in the Buddyfight class.
And my favorite
tournament of the year.
Wow, sign me up!
I can hardly wait.
Before you get too excited,
this is a team competition.
So you'll need to form a
group of two or more students.
Huh, a team?
Baku!
I want you to build my deck.
Sure, but only if you
listen to me, okay?
First time for everything.
You're gonna need
an analyst, too.
Am I right?
What's an analyst?
Something you can eat?
An analyst is a person who
keeps track of all the card data
and recommends play strategies.
In other words,
she's a walking,
talking card dictionary.
Wicked!
We can use that!
So now we have a team.
All that's left to do is
come up with a good name.
Huh?
Let's call it
Rising Tiger.
I think that oughtta catch
their attention, hey, guys?
You sure you want
us on your team?
It's just that
we won't be much help.
Yeah, we're not strong
fighters like you are.
We don't even know
how to build a deck.
Hey, not a problem.
You just need to
make up the numbers,
the rest I'll do myself.
You think you even stand
a chance after yesterday?
Yeah, I mean, that Gao
Mikado guy destroyed Rouga
in just one turn.
He obviously just got lucky.
Beating someone
on your first turn
isn't something you can plan.
That guy just fluked
out is all, trust me.
I think our team name should
be the Mighty Sun Fighters.
Huh?
I'm already the
Mighty Sun Fighter.
You'll be the
Mighty Deck Builder
and you, the Mighty Analyst.
So together we'd be called
the Mighty Sun Fighters.
It's a no brainer.
Super cool, don't you think?
Sounds to me like you just
wanna take all the credit.
No way, Jose.
But I will be the
only one fighting.
Let's keep brainstorming, guys.
The Mighty Sun Fighters
is a stupid name.
Fine, who needs ya?
I'll build my own deck!
How hard can it be
to slap a few cards
together anyway?
Oh, yeah, you think so?
In that case I'll never ever
build a deck for you again.
And I'll form my own team.
Good luck with that.
Come on, boys.
♪
And now to finish them off.
Hey, Geronimo, go
and attack the fighter.
Not bad at all.
For a Dragon Knight deck
it seems fairly
well put together.
(screaming)
Game over.
Winner, Noboru Kodo.
Buddy Cup here I come.
Like I told you,
you're just too strong for me.
Come on, you're up Nitani.
Uh, yeah.
What's with him?
‐Raise the flag.
I fight for Dragon World.
I sense trouble in his future.
Why do you have
to fight about it?
You are gonna regret
running away like this, Baku.
I'm okay.
See?
You're already
regretting it, aren't you?
No, not at all.
I think I just need
something to eat.
Here you go.
It's high in potassium.
Huh?
Hurry up and eat it, young man,
before it spoils.
Okay, don't mind if I do.
Mmm, mmm, mmm.
That did the trick.
As a thanks for this banana I,
the grand master
of all deck builders,
will build your deck.
You really mean it?
This deck building
stuff is easy.
Hey.
This guy here is one
of my favorite monsters.
Yeah, I'm gonna
need this one here,
and this one too
to increase my gauge.
There, my most powerful one yet.
You sure they're all gonna
fit into your deck case?
Nope, not even close.
Didn't think so.
Maybe if I push a little harder.
(ringing)
Kuguru?
She said her house
was supposed to be
around here somewhere, right?
Uh, you mean like that big
one right in front of us?
Oh, yeah.
Man.
Don't tell me she lives here.
What's this?
Ah!
Hi, guys.
Find the place okay?
Yeah, but what did you want
us to disguise ourselves for?
Please, make yourself at home.
Man, this place is huge.
Hey, those are Baku's shoes.
And that's why you're incognito.
So Tetsuya.
What's the
objective of your deck?
That's easy.
It's to win, of course, yo.
Yeah, but how do
you plan to win?
A speedy attack
or defend and then a counter
or maybe a deadly combo deck?
It all sounds good.
How about just giving
me a little of each.
Come on, you can't
have everything.
That would be like
asking a pro sumo wrestler
to be a gymnast.
Nothing's impossible
for Demon Lord Asmodai.
Sumo gymnast!
Boo‐yah.
He went there.
Anyway, you really need
to start with a focus.
Or maybe a specific
card you wanna use.
Hm.
Sure!
I pick Asmodai.
Huh?
How about a deck with
a bunch of Asmodais
to show off their
wicked skills, yo.
Tetsuya.
Oh yeah, and then we
could call it something
like Asmodai's Crazy
Dance Spectacular Deck.
Actually, I'd prefer
something a little edgier.
Not a problem.
I can work with that.
Yeah, sounds good.
What are we doing here again?
I don't know.
First we'll add more Asmodais.
Give me Asmodai's
trends and abilities.
You got it.
And his synergy.
Wow, yo.
He's racing.
So that's a deck
builder at work.
Amazing.
♪
Game over.
Winner, Naboru Kodo.
That's ten wins in a row!
You're just too
strong for us, Naboru.
Okay, let's go again, Maihama.
But I can't.
I've got chess club, remember?
Yeah, and I've got
a test to study for.
All right.
Catch you later, then.
Kid ain't bad.
♪
You could be a
better Buddyfighter.
Slow down, kid.
Hey, kid.
Hey, listen.
Hey.
I watched your fight back there
and I think I can help.
Your deck's well balanced.
But you let your
gauge get too low.
Against a good
fighter it will cost you.
Are you listening?
Why do you keep following me?
Why don't you add an
El Quixote to your deck?
It has a handy ability
to increase your gauge.
I don't actually like
the El Quixote card.
Huh?
What are you talking about?
Okay.
That should do it.
Wow.
You'll get stronger
using your deck
with every match you play.
This is so totally wicked.
There's no way I could
have built a deck like this.
Let's blow this place, Drum.
Huh, why?
Hey, wait!
Look, Kugaru.
Yeah?
I know exactly
what you're up to.
It was worth a try.
Give me one good reason why
you don't like El Quixote.
'Cause he looks weak.
And he's really, really old.
You saw my fights
earlier, right?
I didn't lose a single match.
That's not really saying much.
Yeah, well, my setup's
already good enough as it is.
Huh?
Ah, yeah, I'm super
stoked about my new deck.
Why don't we go try it out?
It's Asmodai and Tetsuya.
I know that buddy monster.
Which can only mean
that that boy there
must be quite a bit
tougher than he looks.
To have a buddy like
that, he must be strong.
No, he's really not.
And the only reason
he's a Buddyfighter
is because Demon Lord
Asmodai asked him to be one.
Hey, I know.
As a warm up match
before the big tournament
why don't I destroy that noob?
Hm.
Really?
Noboru challenged
you to a Buddyfight?
Mhmm.
He challenged me on
my way home yesterday.
We're fighting at
the stage after school.
Come check it.
You do realize he's
the second best fighter
in our grade, right?
And you haven't
had time to practice
with your new deck yet.
So Noboru, huh?
Couldn't ask for
a better opponent.
Hey there, good morning, Gao.
Oh, hi.
With that deck
your odds are good.
Go and get your
first victory, okay?
All right, thanks, Baku.
I'll do my best, yo.
The ABC Cup's just
around the corner
and we've seen some exciting
practice matches lately
as the big day approaches.
Today's game, though,
doesn't promise to be much
as Testuya Kurodake's known
as the worst fighter
in the sixth grade.
But with buddy monster Demon
Lord Asmodai in the house
prepare to be dazzled.
And his opponent today,
also from the sixth grade...
Luminize.
...and ranks
second in his grade,
the lover of
tigers big and small,
Noboru Kodo!
My buddy's Red Baron.
You got this, Noboru!
We'll see.
Come on, you can do it, Asmodai.
You teach that
kitten shirt a lesson.
I'm pretty sure you're supposed
to be cheering for Tetsuya.
But Asmodai's so cool, yo.
Although Noboru has yet
to draw a buddy rare card,
he's shown superior abilities
and who among us can ignore
his commanding presence?
I don't think he should
have any trouble with Tetsuya.
Come on, all you people,
and get down with the beat.
Those neo dancing demons
it's time to defeat.
Yeah.
They've equipped
their core gadgets.
Ready...
Buddyfight!
‐It's time to raise the flag.
I fight for Magic World.
♪
And I fight for Dragon World.
Tetsuya goes first.
Charge and draw.
♪
Time to try out my Asmodai
crazy dance
spectacular strategy.
Oh, please don't use that name.
To give you the kind
of deck you wanted
I had to.
And that meant
I needed to add
four of these cards.
Cast.
I activate Nice One, yo.
He's gonna use it right away?
Playing Nice One,
Testuya can draw two cards.
Wow.
Yo, yo, yo.
Two extra cards, hey,
that's pretty cool.
I'll take all I can get
in my Buddyfight duel.
First I'm gonna call,
and who could be better?
Fallen Angel of Rage,
Beleth to the center.
♪
Beleth, my man, go and get him.
Blow of Power!
♪
End of move.
I'm in total awe.
It was a punishing attack
by Fallen Angel, Beleth.
Your move.
I've dealt with a lot worse.
Now I draw.
Charge and draw.
Dragon Knight
Alexander to the center.
Call.
♪
And Dragon Knight
Masamune to the left.
Call.
♪
Masamune, attack Beleth.
Do your worst, Dragon Knight.
♪
Black Metal Sword!
Oh, curses.
Now, Alexander.
Attack Tetsuya.
Rah!
Gladius breaker!
End of move.
It isn't just Tetsuya's fault.
Magic World itself is weak.
When a high powered
monster's placed at center
you guys are just hopeless.
That's where you're wrong.
Oh, yeah?
And this is where
the real fun begins.
I buddy call my number
one favorite buddy,
Demon Lord Asmodai,
to the center.
You're my favorite, too.
It's show time!
You think a lame size one
monster's gonna help ya?
Huh, Noboru doesn't know.
That's right.
Huh?
Once Asmodai's been called
by discarding one card
he's got the super
useful ability
to destroy any one of
his opponent's monsters
in the field.
Dangerous
Back Drop!
For Sparta!
It's Asmodai's trademark
move, Dangerous Back Drop.
Get ready folks,
'cause he's still
allowed to attack.
Not expecting to have
the center cleared,
Noboru's in big trouble.
But that's impossible.
I call Demon Realm
Warrior, Zepars
to the right and left.
Now you can experience
just how powerful
the Magic World is.
Asmodai attacks Masamune.
Okay.
♪
Here goes.
Tombstone Pile Driver!
And with that Noburo has no
more monsters left on the field.
Could we be in
for an upset here?
Don't make me laugh.
Cast!
Dragonic Thunder!
Destroy the Zepar on the right.
Banzai Blaster.
End of move.
That's why Noboru's
ranked second in his class.
Keeping your damage count
to a minimum like that
takes skill.
Your move.
I'm giving you no mercy.
Draw!
I'll show you why it's
impossible to beat me
once I get serious.
Charge and draw.
I call Dragon Knight
Geronimo to the center.
♪
Paying three gauge
Dragon Knight Geronimo is called
with its 7,000 defense.
He's not making it easy.
Always face an iron type
monster in your center.
Sure, that might be
how an old man fights,
but you'll reduce your
number of losses by doing so.
Huh?
Geronimo's power increases
depending on the
number of Dragon Knights
in the drop zone.
And it also has soul guard,
allowing it to
remain in the field
after it's been destroyed once.
On top of that he
has a special ability
to let him attack twice.
Geronimo, first attack Asmodai.
Go ahead, I'd
like to see you try.
Boomerang Tomahawk!
♪
You're going down.
Get ready.
Huh?
♪
Ah!
End of move.
He has much to learn.
He's a user of Dragon Knights,
and yet seems to have no
clue what they're all about.
His opponent, mind you,
is showing quite a lot of
determination and spunk.
It's clear to see where
this match is headed.
Don't mess with
the amazing skills
of Noboru Kodo.
Yeah, you're doing great.
I'll draw.
But I've got a pretty
amazing deck here,
because Baku's mad
skills as a deck builder
are totally off the charts.
Guess we'll see.
Charge and draw.
Now it's time for the deck
to really begin to shine.
You know I'm gonna cast
Devil Advantage, yo.
I like that spell.
When it's played a
fighter can play one gauge
and bring two 72 pillar monsters
sent to the drop zone
back into their hand.
Nice strategy.
So that means
Asmodai can come back.
Bingo.
Asmodai's defense
isn't the greatest.
That's why I created a deck
that lets him keep
coming back into play
no matter how many
times he's defeated.
Two Asmodai cards have
returned to Tetsuya's hand.
I call Asmodai to the
center and the right.
♪
So, what'd you think?
Magic World's more fun
than you thought, huh?
I discard and activate
Asmodai's ability.
Time to destroy Geronimo.
Okay.
Oh, wow, there it is again.
Asmodai's ability.
Dangerous Back Drop.
Hang on a sec,
Geronimo has soul guard.
Even if destroyed this
ability allows him to come back
as many times as there
are souls beneath him.
If one's just not enough
I'll drop another card, yo.
Ugh.
How do you like me now?
He's destroyed Geronimo again.
How are you supposed
to defend against that?
Asmodai breaks down the defense
and sets up the finishing move.
Not bad for the first
time using his new deck.
Hey, Zepar, now it's up to you.
Go and show 'em what you can do.
That's not gonna happen.
I cast Dragonic Shoot.
I'm not finished yet,
I have another go.
Hey, Asmodai, attack Naboru, yo.
At least I still have
a Dragonic Thunder.
Huh?
Guard against it, Naboru.
Use your Dragonic Thunder.
He can't even if he wanted to.
If I just had one more gauge.
Two Platoon Drop Kick!
After that double Asmodai attack
he's got three life points left.
Begin final phase.
Cast.
♪
You're kidding me.
Diabolical, hardcore!
(yelling)
♪
Owned it!
Game over.
Winner, Tetsuya Kurodake.
♪
He actually did it!
Incredible.
Tetsuya just defeated the second
ranked fighter in grade sixth.
I don't believe it.
Hey, Tetsuya.
Not too bad out there.
It was all thanks to you, yo.
But you were playing the cards.
Unbelievable deck
building, man.
There's no way I could do that.
Sorry for what I said.
Apology accepted, bro.
How about Balle du Soleil?
Huh?
It's French and it
means the Sun Rockets.
I was thinking it could
be our new team name.
So what do you say?
You two have any
problems with that name?
Nope, that works for me.
It sounds way better
than Sun Fighters.
Hey, doesn't my opinion count?
And what about me, you guys?
Okay, we got our sights
set on the ABC Cup.
Let's go, team Balle du Soleil.
Yeah!
I just got unlucky.
I was careless because I
was fighting a total newbie.
Say that enough and
you might believe it.
Huh?
You're that old
guy from yesterday.
Okay, rub it in if you want.
I don't care.
Must have looked pretty funny
seeing a second ranked fighter
defeated by a lowly
unranked challenger.
Your ego's going to
hold you back, kid.
And what exactly makes you an
expert on the subject anyway?
I'd like to offer you my
help, if you'll accept it.
Just who are you, old man?
And why are you following
me around everywhere?
You can call me El Quixote.
♪
A great Dragon Knight
here from Dragon World.
Dragon Knight
El Quixote.
Hello there, I'm Paruko
here to guide you through
the world of Buddyfight.
Do you know about deck builders?
They're our deck
designing specialists.
Using their
extensive knowledge
they analyze card
powers and abilities
to decide which cards should
go into the decks they create.
The strength and
usability of your deck
can really vary a lot
depending on the skill
of your deck builder.
It all sounds
pretty deep, I know.
Just remember
that it's important
to choose your
deck builder wisely.
Can you open a Buddy rare card?
What do you think?
On the next Buddyfight,
the final qualifier
of the ABC Cup begins
and we'll see the top
ranked fighter of his grade,
Zanya Kisaragi,
using the Katana World.
Break past the final qualifier!
Keep on Buddyfighting.