♪
Do you have what it
takes to Buddyfight?
Choose your favorite world
and use special cards
to summon its powerful
monsters into reality.
Challenge other fighters and
buddy call your toughest ally
to fight by your side.
Get ready to
raise the flag!
(grunting)
No fair!
Can I have this dance?
He did it!
A monster with
over 5,000 power.
That's what you get when you
attack with Demon Lord Asmodai.
Hey, where'd he go?
You've fallen
right into my trap.
I pay three gauge and activate
Super Lethal Formation.
Secret Sword Comet!
Oh, dang!
(yells)
(screaming)
♪
Game over.
Winner: Zanya Kisaragi.
♪
All anyone's talking about
these days is the Gaen Cup
sponsored by its namesake,
the Gaen Financial Group.
Today, it was
formally recognized
as an official
Buddyfight tournament
by the
Buddy Card office.
I am proud to announce
of behalf of the board,
that the Buddy Card Office
pledges its full support
to the Gaen Cup.
We hope this leads
to other agencies
giving their
cooperation as well.
"Going green" seems to
be the unofficial theme
of this year's tournament,
so no new facilities
will be built.
Instead, organizers
are transforming
the fighting stage
at Aibo Academy.
I will not
stand for this!
The Amanosuzu Group
has always taken care
of the repairs and maintenance
for all fighting stages
and stadiums in
the metro area.
So, can you tell me why
the Gaen Financial Group
has been chosen
for this latest contract?
(sighs)
Well, because they're
sponsors of the tournament.
So? That still doesn't
mean that they can just go
and do whatever they like.
And another thing,
whose big idea was it
to renovate the
Aibo Academy stage
and use it without
our permission?
You don't know?
You mean you haven't
heard what happened?
Heard what?
Aibo Academy is now
under the control
of the Gaen
Financial Group?
A complete takeover
of the Academy?
The management
structure's changing.
That's all.
Ah, don't worry.
You'll get to keep your current
positions as educators.
For the time
being anyways.
As for the future...
It's you!
You've been
spying on us!
Me? A spy?
Hardly.
I am a beautiful agent!
Kyoya Gaen
is a visionary.
So, naturally, he's
taken a special interest
in the management of
schools for young people.
He merely asked me to do some
research for him is all.
He had me visit and
investigate schools
in countries all
across the globe.
I have to say every place
I went was very charming.
I was asked to examine their
educational policies and ideals.
I even looked into the quality
of their teaching staff.
In my final report,
I recommended Aibo Academy
as the most suitable choice.
Not only is it the best,
but also the most beautiful!
And bow.
You should take
this as a compliment.
You work at the best
school in the world.
All this leaves a horrible
taste in my mouth
like a crusty
day‐old baguette.
I understand how
hard this must be
and I'm sorry, but you
need to accept the fact
that everything
at this Academy,
right down to the
ballpoint pens and thumbtacks
belongs to
Master Kyoya now.
All is as he wants it.
You'll have
to accept that.
You should do your best
to get in the young
tycoon's good graces
so he doesn't trade
you in for newer models.
(growling)
Wow, great poster,
Star Manager!
Yeah, right!
Some dude from Gaen Financial
dropped it off.
They're going all out promoting
this Buddyfight tournament.
Yeah, seems like.
It's gonna be
totally wicked.
I can't wait to find out
which fighters are competing.
I'm so pumped, they
say the whole thing's
gonna be broadcast
live all over the world.
I'm sure Gao received
an invitation,
but I wonder who else.
You haven't heard anything,
have you, Kazane?
Me?
No, I wish.
Seriously,
I'm clueless.
I really hope
Tasuku gets to fight.
Come to think of it,
it'd be cool to see
you in there too, you know?
Where'd she go?
(breathing heavily)
They invited me!
♪
(indistinct chattering)
‐What do you think?
‐Looks awesome!
Our deck
is complete!
‐Alright!
♪
(all chanting "Seifukai")
You, in the cat shirt.
Please step forward.
Uh‐uh‐uh.
It's a tiger.
♪
Oh, yeah!
(applause and cheers)
♪
With the much anticipated
tournament starting tomorrow,
the countdown to
the Gaen Cup is over.
We'll now take you
to a live update
of the preparations
from our reporter
and this year's official
tournament announcer.
Hi there!
I'm Paruko Nanana,
your guide through the
exciting world of Buddyfights!
Don't mind me, I'm
just a little nervous
working with my
hero, Miss Haneda!
Please describe
the atmosphere
at the fighting stage
for our viewers.
Of course!
See for yourself.
The renovations
are finally finished
and everyone is anxiously
awaiting the opening ceremony.
The tournament officially
kicks off at noon tomorrow,
and we'll be bringing
you live coverage
of all the exciting
action from each match.
We hope you'll join us.
♪
This one's no good either.
(growling)
Are we having any
luck over here?
No, not at all.
I tried, but
every single one
of the secret entrances
has been blocked.
I can't access the stage.
I am having
the same problem.
Things are set up
so we can't even
enter the Teacher's Lounge
without special passes.
How dare they go and do this
without even consulting us!
The way things are going,
I'm sure that the stage
has been greatly changed.
Special renovations, huh?
It makes me wonder
what they're up to.
They've got to
be hiding something.
Maybe it's time to
investigate on our own.
Are you saying what
I think you're saying?
We'll unite our powers
to protect the students!
You can let go now.
‐I did.
‐Oh, my bad.
♪
The Gaen Cup
starts today!
Take a look at
my new dress!
I've been saving it for
a super special day!
Tell me how good I look!
Hello?
(growls)
It's time to
get up, mister!
(grunts)
He's gone.
♪
Looks like he took
Drum with him.
Come on, you guys.
What seems to be
the hold up in here?
Breakfast is
starting to get cold.
‐They're not here.
‐What?
Gao left the house
in a hurry hours ago.
‐Really?
‐Why didn't you tell me?
He never leaves
home without breakfast.
I packed
something for him
and his cute little
dragon friend, too.
So good, hungry?
No, thanks.
I can't believe he
hasn't woken up yet.
I know.
He's been like this
ever since he got here.
I'm really
starting to worry.
I don't get it!
He wasn't injured
or anything.
His doctor thinks
it's psychological.
Like maybe something upsetting
or unpleasant happened to him,
which is subconsciously
preventing him from waking up
and keeping him asleep.
What do you
think it is?
I bet Disaster had
something to do with it.
It could be.
Mr. Takihara is looking
into that possibility.
Disaster took Tasuku
and we still don't
even know where he is,
but I promise you
that I'm gonna find out.
(grunts)
Time to take
your temperature.
Hmm?
What gives?
You're supposed
to leave all
the dangerous
investigations to me.
You hear what
I'm saying?
Nurse Modai!
Then I can take care of
winning all the Buddyfights.
If we win, Kiri'll be so stoked,
he'll jump out of bed, yo!
I can't believe
you guys all came!
Like I told you
on the phone,
you're not the only one who's
worried about our friend.
Yeah, bro, I mean, Kiri is
one of the original members
of Team Balle Du Soleil.
Huh?
Yeah, you got
that right!
Let's do it!
We're gonna win this
tournament in his honor
and then he'll get to wake up
with a smile on his face.
♪
Hmm.
Come on, Team
Balle du Soleil!
Let's go get 'em!
‐Yeah!
The first match won't
start for two hours,
but there's already a massive
line in front of the stadium.
Let's go inside
for a live update
of the action
from Paruko.
Hello, everyone!
I'm sure you're all
as anxious as I am
for the tournament to begin.
Believe it or not, I'm
standing just a few feet
from the fighting stage
where all of the
exciting action
will be taking place.
It looks like one of the
fighters is coming out!
Let's see what
he has to say.
Excuse me, can you
tell our viewers
how you're preparing
for the competition?
Just a few
words will do.
Hey, what are you doing?
Ah! Is that soda?
‐Stop it!
‐Tako‐chu!
(static)
(debris falling)
Hmm?
Hey, look!
Is that Kyoyo Gaen?
Yes!
The tournament
sponsor and president
of the Gaen Financial Group
is exiting his helicopter now.
(humming)
Huh?
Oh, you don't say.
Get ready.
The Gaen Cup's
about to begin!
♪
Welcome, everyone.
Glad you could make it.
This is going to
be a lot of fun.
♪
Buddyfighting, as you all
know, is a great card game
that connects people
and links worlds together.
(cheering)
Things are heating up.
Kinda makes you
want to start dancing.
‐Yo, yo, yo, yo!
I don't think I've
ever been so excited.
This is probably the
first time in history
that a Buddyfight tournament
has been broadcast
live all over the world.
It really doesn't
get any cooler than this.
Nin, nin!
I can't help but think
there's an ulterior
motive to all this.
Me too, bro, something's
definitely up, that's for sure.
No matter how dark
things might get,
the mighty sun fighter
will light the way!
You tell 'em, kid.
And lastly, the reason
I'm sponsoring this cup
is to share my favorite
game with all of you.
You ready?
Then let's welcome
our first fighters!
(crowd cheers)
Living up to his
reputation as a thoughtful
and motivating speaker,
that was a fantastic
opening speech by Mr. Gaen.
Next up, the draw to
find out who plays who.
Eight teams have been
invited to participate,
and each team is made
up of three fighters.
Let's see who
will be up first.
While they're drawing,
I should take a moment
to point out that the first
team to score two victories
will be the winner.
The suspense
is just crazy.
Talk about being on
the edge of your seat, huh?
Any moment now,
here it comes!
♪
First team: Balle du Soleil!
‐Huh?
‐I don't like this.
It's way better than
having to wait around, man!
(cheers)
What do you know?
It's home crowd favorite,
Team Balle du Soleil
led by Gao Mikado
from our very own
Aibo Academy's
Junior School.
Now, let's listen to
see who they'll be facing.
It's Team Goddess!
I've never heard of them.
Let's find out who these
mysterious fighters are.
(giggles)
It seems that the
brave Mr. Mikado and I
are bound together
by the power of fate.
There it is!
The first match of the
first ever Gaen Cup will be
between Team Balle du Soleil
and Team Goddess.
Don't go away!
After this break, we'll
have all the action for you.
Do your best, Gao,
and make me proud.
Crush 'em good, Z.
We'll go get set up over at
the Buddy Pit, alright, bro?
I know you'll
win this one.
Thanks for letting me
take the first match, guys.
I won't let you
down, I promise.
No problem, yo.
Wait, don't do it.
I actually think
that I should go first.
‐Huh?
‐You're stressing me out.
You saw how excited
the audience is out there.
It was like being in
one of my live shows.
(cheering)
If the crowd's
supporting our team,
then that's great,
but we could still
get overwhelmed
by the atmosphere.
I'm worried that
we might lose
without being able to utilize
even half of our full power.
Yeah, I get it.
I think you'll agree that
at times like these,
the person who
has the most calm
and has the most self‐control
should step up.
I hear ya!
The first battle
should be yours.
Let's go do this,
Tsukikage.
Nin.
They've changed
up the order.
Now Zanya's
going first.
My big brother will
get the ball rolling!
♪
Are you okay?
You have that look
on your face again.
It's kinda hard
to explain,
but I just have
a bad feeling
about Zanya going
up for this fight.
Team Balle du Soleil's fighter
is now entering the stage.
It's none other than
the top ranked player
in Aibo Academy's Junior
School: Zanya Kisaragi.
And with him is
his buddy monster,
the electrifying
ninja, Tsukikage.
Let's see who will be
up first for Team Goddess.
What's going on?
What's with
all the bells?
(vocalizing)
♪
♪ Amanosuzu proves the best ♪
Two guesses
who that is.
♪
(giggling)
Ta‐dah, I'm here.
Who else were you
expecting, silly?
Obviously not
someone this pretty.
(whimpering)
(glass breaks)
As if you
didn't already know,
that's the young heiress
of the world renowned
Amanosuzu Group,
Lady Suzuha.
The only daughter of a
successful industrialist,
Lady Suzuha inherited her
dad's competitive nature,
which she demonstrated
in her most recent match
against Gao Mikado
of Team Balle du Soleil.
♪
I‐‐I didn't think
I'd be fighting a girl.
(crash)
What's with him?
Big Z!
Of course, I knew
something was up!
I should have realized Team
Goddess would be all girls.
Girls totally
freak him out.
What do you think?
Is there anything
we can do to help him?
Come on!
Pull yourself
together out there!
♪
(shouts)
I'm extremely
disappointed
that I won't
be fighting Gao.
But I'm a lady, so I'll
challenge you to a duel.
♪
A girl's glove just
touched me in my face!
(crash)
What a terribly
rude boy you are.
I'm going to enjoy
defeating you.
Hold on to your seats!
The first match of the
Gaen Cup is about to begin.
‐I'm ready, Sebastian.
‐My lady.
♪
Prepare yourself
for a miracle.
Angel Queen Serenade!
Luminize!
Hurry up, Z, we're
all counting on you.
♪
Secret and silent but
you still can hear the sound
of my mighty sword.
Luminize, Kisaragi
Ninja Arts Type Two.
Buddyfight!
(crowd cheering)
‐Time to raise the flag!
I fight for Magic World.
♪
And I fight for
Katana World.
♪
Zanya's taking
the first turn.
Charge and draw.
Hate to say it, but this
is gonna be entertaining.
I call Stealth Ninja Kirikakure
Saizo to the center area.
♪
Attack m'lady‐‐
I mean, the lady.
Keep it together, Zanya.
If the guy needs
some advice with girls,
he should have
just asked me, yo.
I doubt that.
Zanya caused
two damage points
to Lady Suzuha with
Kirikakure Saizo,
and then called Final Phase
and set a Super
Lethal Formation spell
before the end
of his move.
The action never stops!
Miss Pretty has just called
three monsters at once.
With the spell,
she increased her gauge
and the number
of cards in her hand.
Her monsters
are on attack.
Sea green!
♪
Heed the blinding
blade of light!
(grunts)
Lucky for him, Zanya only
suffered one damage point
from Magic Knight of
Light, Licht's attack
and he neutralized
Magician of Glass,
Will Glassart's
attack by using
Art of Body Replacement!
Your move.
I better try and focus.
I can't lose a
match cause of this.
Draw.
Charge and draw!
Then, I buddy call
to the left.
♪
Nin.
With a buddy gift, he
regains one life point.
I call Electron Ninja
Shiden to the right!
♪
Using Shiden's ability,
I increase the number
of cards in my hand.
Should he really be using
up his gauge at this point?
And I thought ninjas were
supposed to be stealthy.
Zanya's equipping
Ninja Blade Kurogachi!
Huh, what a
bonehead move.
The Super Lethal
Formation's effect
has driven the power
of his ninjas way up!
♪
(grunting)
Lady Suzuha's center
is now wide open!
Prepare to lose!
♪
She's looking at me.
(grunting)
Hey, how come he didn't
attack the fighter?
Maybe he has some
greater plan in mind.
No, he doesn't.
Our fair lady goes
for it with a buddy call,
and takes full advantage
of her cards' abilities
by calling out two
very powerful monsters.
You're about to feel the true
force of my Noble Magician Deck.
The power of which
you've never seen!
Now, I cast.
The incredible
Great Spell,
My Grandfather Clock.
(clock chiming)
She used it!
It's the super
powerful great spell!
(chuckles)
You've just fallen
right into my trap.
He doesn't have enough.
Huh?
Ah, where's all my gauge?
He doesn't have
enough gauge remaining
to activate his
Super Lethal Formation.
I wondered why he
was using it all up
on Shiden's
Cyber Analyze ability.
(groans)
You got to hang on!
Faced with Lady Suzuha's
vicious assault,
there's nothing Zanya
can do but take it!
(yells)
Come on, big brother!
You have to find
a way through this!
Because of My Grandfather
Clock's ability,
it's her turn
once again.
(laughing)
♪
The Baroness of
transportation equipment
continues her fierce attack,
and poor Zanya finds himself
in an inferno of doom.
‐How disappointing.
‐What now?
I was hoping for more
in the opening fight.
This is turning out
to be quite mediocre.
Well, this is Team Balle "dumb"
Soleil we're talking about.
(snickering)
Go on, Mary Sue.
Finish him off.
Stay away from me!
(giggling)
(whimpering)
Another girl!
No, stop!
(screaming)
Real smooth, Zanya.
♪
(crowd cheers)
Game over.
Winner: Suzuha Amanosuzu.
(laughing)
That was rather easy.
Girls freak me out.
Team Goddess takes
the first win.
If Team Balle du Soleil wants
to take this tournament,
it's gonna be a
tough hill to climb.
(growling)
It's time for...
Tasuku and Gao's...
‐Card of the day!
The card we're gonna
talk about today
is called Drum Bunker
Dragon "Duel Wield".
You got to call this
card on top of Drum.
It's my buddy's
super attack form.
It has 12,000 power,
plus a critical of four,
and it even has the
ability to penetrate.
And it has Soul Guard, so even
if defeated once, you're okay.
Building a deck around
Drum is the way to go!
So, what do
you think, guys?
You think you can
open up one of these?
You'll never know
until you try!
♪
Next time,
Gao takes the stage
in our second match
against Team Goddess.
There's no way
Balle du Soleil can lose now.
Wait, Gao's not fighting?
Next episode, "The Dancing
Demon Takes on Medusa!"
Join us for
a Buddyfight!