Do you have what it
takes to Buddyfight?
Choose your favorite world,
and use special cards
to summon its powerful
monsters into reality.
Challenge other fighters,
and Buddy Call your toughest
ally to fight by your side.
Get ready to raise the flag.
♪
I can't really decide.
I want to make sure
I get a good one.
♪
Come on, we don't
have all day, yo.
The trick's not to give
yourself time to think about it.
Just watch me, see that?
♪
What did you get?
Anything good?
Seriously?
I got all monsters again?
Unbelievable,
and statistically improbable.
That's it, I'm gonna
make the best deck ever.
I'm a master deck builder,
I can deal with this.
♪
Hey, Gao?
Would you mind
picking mine for me?
You want me to do it?
Our class is almost
over, Mr. Hyoryu.
Please hurry and choose.
Time's a wasting.
Close your eyes, and grab one.
♪
Well, what are you waiting for?
Okay.
♪
Is this for real?
You got a special
rare card, bro!
Demon Wolf Fenrir, 10,000
attack, 7,000 defense.
And, woah, a critical of six.
It's a size three
monster from Legend World.
Did that actually just happen?
Yep.
♪
This is the best day of my life.
Why don't we just add
some more monsters?
We can't, that would
totally throw off the balance.
How about putting
in a card like this?
No, I don't think so.
Why not try this one?
It could be used as a combo
after sending Fenrir
to the drop zone.
What do you think?
You know, it's not a bad idea.
If used right, it could make
for a totally fearsome combo.
I must say, it looks
like Legend World
is a perfect fit for you, Kiri.
Wow, you really think so?
Yeah.
To prove it, why don't
we have a Buddyfight?
Sure!
Are you kids still here?
Class was dismissed hours ago,
it's time you all went home.
Okay.
Hey, how about we
continue this at Castle?
I wish they were this
eager doing their homework.
'Sup?
You're 20 minutes late again.
There was a mime.
I love mimes.
I hear you're slapping
together a pretty awesome deck.
I can't wait to check it out.
Well, I've had some help.
Lose the modesty, bro.
You're getting pretty
sweet at building decks.
I agree, it's hard to believe
you only started Buddyfighting
after transferring to Aibo.
You serious, nobody
ever told me that.
Oh, poor Baku, always
the last to know.
You know, Kiri
and I actually met
before he came to our school.
You really remember that, Gao?
How could I forget it?
I mean, you are
my bud, after all.
Yeah, of course.
Cool, Gao really
thinks of me as his bud?
Look who's here.
Hey, good to see you.
Same.
He'd like to use
the stage, please.
Sure, no problem.
So, who are you
fighting today, dude?
Actually, Gao's
gonna be the tuner.
Kiri built a new deck,
and we want to take
it for a test drive.
Thanks a lot for
letting us use the stage.
No sweat.
Let me set it up for you.
(phone ringing)
I think it's mine.
It's my dad?
If someone else wants
to use the stage first,
go ahead, I'll be
back in a sec.
While you're waiting,
want to fight me?
You're on!
Hey Dad, what's up?
Kiri, I hate to tell
you over the phone,
but I've been transferred.
Please say you're kidding.
I'm sorry, son, but this means
you'll have to change schools.
Change schools?
You can do your
studies anywhere.
In a few months, you'll
hardly remember that place.
But I've made some
great friends here!
There's nothing I can do, I've
made the arrangements already.
We'll be leaving this weekend,
so you'll need to pack
your things tonight.
What? This weekend?
It's not so bad,
you've done it before.
Let's talk later, son.
But it's not the same
as last time, I think.
Okay, Drum, hit that
Sheila Vanna with all you got!
I've got a lot!
End of move.
Nice one!
Your move.
Two can play at that game.
Now you get to see
how good my game is.
Draw!
Charge and draw!
Check it, I Buddy Call Bladewing
Phoenix to the center position.
I'm watching you, you
ill‐mannered mongrel!
♪
She does have one
pretty choice Buddy, huh?
No doubt, let's see
if he can help her win.
So, Kiri, who was
that on the phone?
Well, actually...
Go attack Gao!
Release raptor blades!
Drum, help me out!
Sorry, kid, I thought
he'd come after me first!
Do you like that?
Well, how about some more?
Go on, Phoenix, attack
Gao one more time.
Raptor blades!
Gao and Kazane are having
a pretty good match, huh?
Yeah, bro.
Battles between these two
are always a ton of fun,
and super exciting for
the spectators to watch.
They're awesome rivals, bro.
You really think they're rivals?
They only met a few weeks ago.
Time doesn't factor into it.
It's because their skills
are so well‐matched.
Not just that, it also
comes down to the chemistry
between you and your character.
Some people you only meet
once, but never forget,
and others you've
known a long time,
but don't leave a
lasting impression.
So then, which one am I to Gao?
I wish I was his rival.
I have some sad news,
class, unfortunately,
today will be Kiri Hyoryu's
last day at our school.
Although I was only
here a short time,
I really enjoyed being a part of
this class, so thanks, everyone.
I'm going to miss you all a lot.
Hey, Kiri!
You almost left
without taking this.
Thanks, Akira!
Thanks for bringing
it down here.
Well, we are friends, aren't we?
Mhm.
Hey, Akira!
Long time.
Yeah, I guess so.
It's me, Kiri, we were
in the same class until
three months ago when I had to
leave school, do you remember?
Oh, yeah, I think
I remember you.
But, to be honest,
I can't really be sure.
But I thought you said
that we were friends.
I did?
Are you serious?
Well, it's about time.
No, I'm not doing anything.
Cool, be right there.
Sorry, I got to get going.
Gotta go hang out
at my friend's place.
♪
It'll be just like before,
as soon as I transfer
to a different school,
I'll drift apart from everyone.
Now you're done for!
Time for final phase!
Cast!
♪
Impact!
Gargantua Punisher!
♪
I was afraid of that!
Game over.
Winner, Gao Mikado.
♪
That's what I'm talking about.
That's one way to
finish your opponent.
You know it.
Well, it looks like
you're up next, Kiri.
I'm counting on
another memorable fight.
I have to do this.
I'll give it everything I got.
I'll put on a show so impressive
that Gao will never
be able to forget me.
A Buddyfight for the ages.
I don't know.
Am I really gonna pull
off something like that?
♪
I mean, Gao has
fought and defeated
so many powerful fighters.
It's pure accident
that your triple attack
worked on Bahamut.
End of move.
Who am I kidding, he won't
remember fighting against me.
I don't even have a Buddy.
Let's face off again
sometime, Kazane.
Sure, sounds like a blast.
Our matches rock.
I guess because you're
my rival, eh, Gao?
Yeah.
♪
There's no way I could beat
him fighting like I do now.
But maybe I could defeat Kazane.
If I can beat Kazane, who
Gao thinks of as his rival,
then I'm sure he'll remember
that match for a long time.
♪
Sorry it took so long.
You ready to hit
that stage, Kiri?
Hey, Kazane, listen up,
I challenge you to a Buddyfight.
Huh?
Sure.
Paruko Nanana here, welcome,
once again, to another
exciting Buddyfight.
Wherever there are
matches being played,
you can bet yours
truly will be there,
commentating on every heroic
move and electrifying turn.
Today's match features
Aibo Academy students,
Kiri Hyoryu of sixth grade,
and Kazane Fujimiya
of the fifth grade.
Kazane, who also goes
by the name "Wind"
is well known for being
a tough dynamic player,
and she's earned
the top position
on the Castle Shop ranking.
At the other end
of the scale is Kiri,
with no significant experience.
So on paper, this fight
looks pretty one‐sided.
What's up with him, anyway?
He said he was going
to fight you, didn't he?
Relax, it's all good.
Kiri can fight
against me anytime.
I've been wondering, has Kiri
been acting a little strangely?
Maybe, I guess.
♪
Now let's see your
potential, Kiri.
♪
Buddyfight!
Oh yeah!
Time to raise the flag!
I fight for Dungeon World!
I fight for Legend World,
and my Buddy Demon Wolf, Fenrir.
A Demon Wolf?
That is just wicked.
Let's make this
a fun fight, 'kay?
♪
It can't be a friendly,
I have to make sure I win this,
or I'll never be Gao's rival.
Charge and draw!
I call the pesky Gummy
Slime to the center.
Now go attack the fighter.
Gummy!
(squeaking)
End of move.
In your face!
So what sort of deck did
Kiri put together anyways?
Let's just say,
if he's in a jam,
it'll wield tons of power, bro.
Good luck, Kiri, make us proud.
Draw.
Charge and draw!
I call Corpse
Swallower, Hraesvelgr
to the center position!
♪
I've never seen one up close.
Hraesvelgr's ability
allows for another card
to be drawn when an Asgard card
is discarded from the hand.
♪
Time to get serious.
I call Frost Giant,
Hrimthurs to the right.
♪
Let's go Hraesvelgr,
attack that Gummy Slime!
And as for you, Hrimthurs,
attack the fighter!
♪
End of move.
Nice job.
Graciousness can wait.
Focus your energy on
your next move, Missy.
I'm way ahead of you, Blade.
Your move.
Okay, this is the part where
I crank it up a few notches.
♪
I'm gonna discard
one card from my hand,
and equip Brave
Equipment, Glory Seeker.
That thing has a
critical of three.
All right, I call Magical
Fortress, Orser Kleinz
to the right.
My darling, how
may I be of service
to you this beautiful day?
It blows my mind that
she even has one of those.
What's so special
about that one?
His ability is activated
by returning an adventurer
and a dungeon enemy from
the drop zone to the deck.
Just watch and see.
♪
She increased her gauge.
And I get one more draw.
I call Dragonblade Wielding
Sheila Vanna to the left!
♪
Let's play.
You should know all
about this, bro.
I mean, we did build your
Dungeon World deck together.
What's with these monsters?
Come on, I know you know.
Adventurer and dungeon enemy.
If I remember right,
decks are always stronger
when they're built off
of one of those two types.
Yeah, and since
I'm an adventurer,
your deck focuses on
amazing monsters like me.
But Kazane's deck has both.
She's got dungeon enemy
monsters like Gummy Slime
and Bladewing Phoenix,
and adventurer monsters, too.
And yet, it's all built
around one single monster.
So this deck
is built to take advantage
of Orser Kleinz's skills?
It's not just Orser's abilities
I can take advantage of.
Orser, and Sheila!
Go link attack Kiri!
Delighted!
With boundless pride!
♪
If there's an
adventurer in the field,
Sheila Vanna will get them.
♪
No way.
If there were a dungeon enemy
in the current situation,
then the critical would be
increased by two whole points.
So I guess even Sheila Vanna
can use its skills with
the power of this deck.
Here I come!
Not so fast!
Cast Power of Mythology!
♪
Oh man!
End of move!
I cannot hide my disappointment.
I never expected this.
Kazane's deck is actually
rather incredible.
Looks like you're not the
only Miss Smartypants around.
He's right.
It's gonna be pretty tough
for Kiri to beat Kazane now.
I just don't see it.
I wouldn't be so sure.
You're forgetting, Kiri put
a lot of effort into
assembling his deck.
So I don't think he's gonna
be defeated quite that easily.
She's really skilled.
The way things are going,
I don't know how
I'm going to beat her.
I really thought I had
a good chance at winning this.
I just can't let
myself be defeated.
I mean, you are
my bud, after all.
I have to make Gao notice me.
♪
But if I want that to happen,
I gotta win this match.
♪
I call Hrimthurs
to the center area,
and cast Set Spell Gleipnir.
♪
A set spell, really?
No way, he's moved his
size 3 Demon Wolf Fenrir
from the drop zone to the soul.
Okay, Hrimthurs, the one
on the center attacks Kazane,
and the one on the right,
you attack Orser Kleinz!
♪
Sorry, my lady!
Now I'll cast Breathen Gard.
Go and take out Gleipnir.
Say what, he just
destroyed his own set spell!
He's using his
Breathen Gard too soon.
Of course, why
didn't I see that?
By destroying Gleipnir,
he can call a monster from
his soul without paying a cost.
See, I knew Kiri had it in him.
Oh yeah, kid's got game.
Yes, he just called Wolf Fenrir
without having to pay
the five gauge cost.
That size three monster
has got a critical of six!
One life point recovered
with a Buddy gift.
That is one big doggy.
♪
Kyoya sure was right, he's good.
What an awesome move, I've never
seen a combo like that before!
This is no time to be flattering
your opponent, my dear!
Where's my first prey?
The fighter!
I guess you mean me, right?
Demon Wolf Fenrir's
unique ability allows it
to attack immediately, even when
called with Gleipnir's effect.
♪
I'm gonna win, and with
the card that Gao picked for me.
That'll make him proud.
And if I do, I'm sure Gao
and I will stay friends.
♪
Your time has come!
And I cast Divine
Protection of Shalsana!
♪
She nullified the attack!
That was a pretty close one.
End of move.
Oh no.
What a move.
Sweet, she stopped
a choice attack.
Yeah, pretty
impressive for a human.
He okay?
Once again...I'm going to lose.
Hey, look alive over there,
I'm calling Bladewing
Phoenix to the right!
A Buddy gift helps her
regain one life point.
I shall cut down anyone
displaying rudeness!
Okay, let's do a link
attack against Fenrir,
with Sheila Vanna and Blade!
♪
Raptor blades!
I guess now I'm not gonna
have any friends again.
♪
By having a dungeon enemy
like Blade in the field,
the penetrating attack
will reach three critical!
♪
And if that's not bad enough,
Blade has a double attack!
How careless of you.
What a waste.
So much for leaving
a lasting impression.
♪
Now it's my turn to have fun.
Glory Seeker will
finish you off!
If only I fought better.
♪
Game over, winner,
Kazane Fujimiya.
I did it!
Kiri had a pretty
good fight overall.
I'll say, especially
when you consider
that he just built his
Legend World deck today.
Yeah, when you put it like that.
Look at him.
♪
He's gonna be awesome.
Definitely a boost to disaster.
Hey, thanks, that
was a total blast.
♪
Morning, yo; Up for
another super awesome day?
You bet!
Oh, hey, how about we sit
together in first period?
You know you're in the
class next door, right?
My bad, yo!
Hey, guys.
And a good morning to you.
You're late, dude.
I wonder why Kiri
isn't here yet.
He's usually in
class before me.
He's always on
time for everything.
Yeah, he did go straight
home on Friday after he lost.
Maybe he was getting
sick or something?
I should go see.
I'll swing by his place later.
Okay, everybody,
please take your seats.
I have some news for you today.
Your friend and classmate,
Kiri Hyoryu is transferring
to a different school.
His father was promoted
to regional manager,
so his family has to move.
(gasping)
So, when will he
be leaving school?
From what the principal told me,
I believe he's already left.
Bummer, how could he leave
without even telling us?
I don't understand
why he would do that.
Kiri.
♪
Huh?
Hello there, Kiri Hyoryu.
Are you looking
for a new friend?
♪
It's time for...
Tasuku and Gao's...
Card of the Day.
Today, we'll introduce you
to the Demon Wolf,
Fenrir combination.
Fenrir is a super strong
monster with a critical of six,
but it costs five
gauge to bring it out.
So, to get around this, you can
place Fenrir in the soul
of the set spell Gleipnir,
and destroy it.
Then you can call
it with no cost.
There's a little
more to this combo,
but we'll have to get to
those details next time.
So what do you think, guys?
Think you can open
up one of these?
You'll never know until you try!
♪
Next time, a strange
letter arrives from Kiri,
and Gao decides
to pay him a visit.
When they finally meet, Kiri's
carrying a Dark Core deck case!
Next episode,
Kiri Strikes Back.
You don't want to miss this one.