Do you have what it
takes to Buddyfight?
Choose your favorite world,
and use special cards
to summon its powerful
monsters into reality.
Challenge other fighters,
and Buddy Call your toughest
ally to fight by your side.
Get ready to raise the flag.
Combine, Calcula‐cross!
Einder.
Zweider.
Dreider.
Complete!
Infinite Robot Mathematic!
Four Arithmetical
Operation Sword.
Infinite power!
Four Arithmetical
Operation Slash!
Sword of Damocles, final answer!
Good guys always win.
You haven't seen the last of me!
Game over.
Winner: Captain Answer.
♪
There is no question.
Amazingly, after
all these years,
we are once again in his debt.
♪
Okay class, as you know,
Miss Honagaso will be away
on maternity
leave for a while,
so you're going to have
a temporary replacement
for first period Math.
I'm sure I don't
need to remind you
to be on your Aibo best
behavior for our new teacher.
So what's the new
teacher's name?
Of course, the teacher's
name is Elf Kabala.
An elf?
Like a kind of sprite?
(chatter)
Wow, cool.
All right.
♪
Who can calculate
the area of my wings?
Are there any volunteers?
(chatter)
Here we are.
Principal Ikarino.
Morning, I'd like to introduce
you to your new math teacher.
I call to the center, the
one, the only, Elf Kabala!
Lights!
What's going on?
Hello, little people.
For those who
weren't daydreaming,
you just heard that
my name is Elf Kabala.
And I am...beautiful!
♪
Let's see, I was at the gym
and didn't have time to make
a lesson plan for today, but...
I'll let you start
with something easy.
Why don't you approximate
how many chest presses
I can do in only one minute?
Oh man.
We got six months of this?
That snooze button's messed up.
♪
Hey, Gao, what're you doing
in my first class, yo?
I should be asking you that.
Your class is next
door, space case.
Aw, he's not a space case.
Sometimes.
I'm just sleepy, yo.
Yo.
Hiya, today I'm in your
class, can you dig it?
Chill out, some of us are
trying to learn, like me.
That's a good one.
They're just like
he said they'd be.
Wait, I know.
Buddyfighting is popular
at this academy, right?
I'd sure love to see
some Buddy monsters
fighting up in here.
There's only one student
in our class with a Buddy.
Yeah, that's our friend, Gao.
Ding a ling, I've
got a Buddy too, yo.
Yeah, I'll take you on!
Think again!
Remember, your studies
always come first.
Only through vigorous learning
will you acquire
enough knowledge
to be strong, successful
Buddyfighters.
I'm counting on you, now,
and if anyone acts up,
send them directly to
my office, you hear me?
Right.
I was really hoping to try
out my Ultimate Dungeon Deck.
I was getting seriously stoked.
Ultimate Dungeon
Deck... Deck... Deck.
Did I hear you right?
You have an
Ultimate Dungeon Deck?
Careful, boy!
An adjective like that
can't be taken lightly!
I will teach you the true
meaning of the word Ultimate,
young man!
Watch and learn.
Because...
you're about to be enlightened.
♪
What?
I don't like the look of this.
Something weird is going on.
I'm totally in
the dark here, bro.
In that case,
I'll turn these on.
♪
I really wasn't
expecting a battle stage.
I am the unexpected!
I had this masterpiece
specially built for my own use.
It's called the Dungeon Stage!
He had it built
just for himself?
You know what that means.
He's a Buddyfighter too.
Guilty as charged.
I've weathered the storm
of countless battles.
When I was young, I
was rash and headstrong,
but in time, I adapted my ways.
The years have been good to me.
So, are we about ready to begin?
I don't think so, people.
You can't start
without Paruko Nanana!
You weren't going
to have a Buddyfight
without little old me, were you?
It's okay, I'll get
over it eventually.
Go ahead, young lady,
I could use the free PR.
Let's show them what we got.
We don't have to stay
and watch this, do we?
Let's run for it.
♪
Weird.
I don't get it, what happened?
You can't escape;
this is the Dungeon Stage.
Unless one of you
manages to defeat me,
nobody's getting out of here.
But I have a date.
No fair.
What a shocking turn of events.
If Principal Ikarino
doesn't lose,
then these students will
be stuck in this dungeon
for all eternity, never to
see the outside world again.
Wait a second,
I'm in the same boat!
Hear that?
Guess it's up to us, Drum.
I do some of my best
work under pressure, kid.
I'm up for the challenge.
♪
Hm, things are starting
to get interesting.
♪
What gives, why aren't I
getting first crack at him?
Where's the love?
What do you think, pal?
Does Gao have it in him or what?
I hope so, for our sakes.
Me too.
Don't lose, Gao,
we're counting on you!
Do we have any idea what the
principal's Buddy is like, bro?
No, I mean, we only just learned
that he's a Buddyfighter
five minutes ago.
I bet it's a really
rare monster.
Hey, Gnarly, yeah, it's me,
I'm at the Dungeon now;
I'm teaching a class.
No, not a yoga class.
You were always a goof.
Who's Gnarly?
Depends what you mean by gnarly.
Human slang is so confusing.
No way, as if!
I wish I was there.
Okay, I'll be waiting.
Come forth, my Buddy!
♪
Bats!
(laughing)
Disastrous Dawn,
Great Wizard and Ruler of
the Labyrinth of Despair.
♪
I am the Demon Lord, Gagnar.
The principal's Buddy
arrives in terrifying fashion!
You know, I could really
do without the bats.
Demon Lord?
Bat brain, long time,
how you been doing?
Hey!
You're just in
time for the show!
Up to no good, huh?
I'm an angel compared to you.
♪
A‐Dawg?
You're really friends with
that evil looking monster, yo?
♪
They're friends?
The Demon Lords?
Funny.
So let me guess why
you called me down here.
You'd like me to
demonstrate some of my
demonic educational guidance for
these impertinent little brats,
am I right?
Yes, these kids need to learn
the true value of
a good education.
They all want the rewards
without putting in
the required effort.
Nothing comes easy,
except to demons.
♪
To be honest, I
hope Gao wins this
so we can get out of here and
I can catch my afternoon soap.
However, despite my feelings,
I'll be announcing impartially,
because I know it's
the right thing to do.
Okay, you ready?
Yeah.
If you take a chance
and reach for the sky,
the clouds will unmask the sun!
Now, luminize, Brave Soleil!
Presumptuous challenger,
I'm going to teach
you a valuable lesson.
But first, luminize!
Prepare for
the Dangerous Dungeon!
Time to Buddyfight.
You call that announcing?
Put your heart into it!
Yes, sir.
Buddy!
Fight!
Come on, one more time!
Buddy!
Fight!
Not hearing it!
Buddy!
Fight!
I can't hear you!
Buddy!
Fight!
Loud and proud!
Looks like we could
be here a while.
Yeah.
Fight!
Goodness, I wonder when the
principal will be returning.
We were supposed
to meet right here.
It's unusually quiet in there.
Where on Earth
has everyone gone?
Hello, you're not going to
jump out and scare me, are you?
It's time to raise the flag!
I fight for Dungeon World!
I couldn't have said
it better myself!
Come on, Gao, you can take him!
Do it for us!
So until this kid wins,
I must stay down here
and watch ad nauseam?
Oh, why me?
Mr. Ikarino has the first move!
Charge and draw!
I call to the center
Bronze Golem, Jaish.
♪
Go attack the fighter!
End of move.
Looks like Ikarino is
gonna play it old school.
You mean he's going to use
some special warrior moves
and ancient techniques?
Not exactly, you'll
have to wait and see.
Your move.
Now draw!
Charge and draw!
I call to the right,
Craftsman, Baku.
Look at that.
Crazy, I'm seeing double.
It's one of the
totally rad cards
Drum picked up in Dungeon World.
Definitely one of my faves.
I call to the left,
Dancing Magician, Tetsuya.
♪
Feel the beat, yo!
Sweet, do you think
he'd sign a card for me?
Hi!
Yo, yo, yo!
Hey!
Yo, yo, yo, yo!
Oh yeah!
Too bad it's not
a... dance fight.
I discard one of
the cards in my hand,
and equip Brave
Equipment, Glory Seeker.
Baku and Tetsuya,
do a link attack!
Boo‐yah.
Relax, guys, I
think he means them.
This Golem's going down.
Bigger they are,
harder they fall.
♪
When Tetsuya and
I do a link attack,
the gauge increases by one, bro.
And with yours truly around,
Baku gets to break
out his double attacks.
It's hammer time!
Let's get Ikarino, I'll join
in too with my Glory Seeker!
Take this!
(yelling)
End of move.
Another of those moves
and you've got this, Gao.
You rock.
He is pretty good.
Your move.
You're better
than you look, kid.
So am I, I draw!
I'm about to teach him
a lesson he'll never forget.
Charge and draw, I cast!
Here comes
Cecilia's Spell Disarm!
Not that!
Time to enter the fray, Gnarly.
Let me at 'em.
I Buddy Call Gagnar
to the center.
♪
Demon Lord, Gagnar's
lecture is in session.
With Gagnar's ability,
the cards in my gauge
are returned to my deck,
and three new cards
are charged to my gauge.
I'll even give you some wingmen.
I call Fate Skeleton,
to the right and left!
♪
Your skill can only take
you so far, oh brash one.
But you're about
to meet your destiny.
For my magical powers
will consume you!
Skeleton on the right,
attack Tetsuya!
(yelling)
Kaboom.
Poor Tets, he was so young.
Hey, I'm still alive, yo.
Skeleton on the
left, attack Gao.
♪
Is it just me, or is
the Dungeon getting smaller?
I'll squash you like a bug.
♪
You okay?
End of move.
Amazing!
Demon Lord, Gagnar took
four life points from Gao
in just one blow.
That what you had in mind?
To the letter.
Let's see how Gao
responds to that.
Your move.
I'm not done yet.
I still got a few
friends to help me out.
Draw!
Charge and draw.
I call to the left,
Sage, Kuguru.
♪
Hey, it's me!
Cool outfit,
mine's better, though.
Baku, Kuguru, link attack
against Demon Lord, Gagnar!
As you wish.
Leave it to us.
Let's go Miss Brainy.
Please refer to me as Sage.
♪
Their love seems to
be having some effect.
Gao's gauge and life points
are magically increasing!
♪
(cheering)
Why don't you ever hold hands?
That's not us, bro.
Those are just cards that
happen to look like us.
That's right.
Baku would never
want to do that.
There's no need
to be embarrassed.
Love is everywhere.
What's more,
love is beautiful!
Enough.
Let's just skip
that move next time.
Yeah, that's a good call.
If you two have
finished your squawking,
let's get on with the fight.
If there's one thing I can't
stand, it's stall tactics!
Looks like they're kind
of getting under his skin.
I cast my Dungeon Explosion!
♪
Love, here one
minute, gone the next.
The crowd's getting restless.
They're angry about
Principal Ikarino's
harsh excessive attack.
You know, I've always
been partial to a good
old‐fashioned romance plot.
♪
What's wrong?
All this love stuff's
gonna make him hurl.
No, that's not it.
Our boy's just hungry.
Between love and lunch,
I'd take lunch any day.
♪
Hey!
What are you doing?
I hope you love your lunch!
Draw!
Charge and draw!
Demon Lord, Gagnar,
I call on you once again
to educate these young ones!
Let me at them.
Ready for some more?
It's time you
learned some manners.
I cast, Divine
Protection of Shalsana!
The light!
(yelling)
What do you think you're doing?
It was a counter spell, why
don't you do something about it?
Are you telling me
how to play this game?
So what if I am?
I guess this is a good time
to take a brief intermission.
Those are grownups?
Don't look now, but the Fate
Skeletons are attacking Gao!
(grunting)
End of move.
Gao's down to just
three life points.
If he doesn't defeat Demon Lord,
Gagnar during this turn,
it's game over, man!
And we'll miss pizza
Thursdays in the cafeteria!
Hey, Drum, your turn!
I call to the
right, Brave Drum!
What now, kid?
I take away one
card from my hand,
and equip Brave
Equipment, Glory Seeker.
Look out, he's coming!
He's got spunk!
Okay, Drum, let's
link attack Gagnar!
(grunting)
Time for Rock‐Paper‐Scissors.
You wouldn't dare!
If Gao wins Rock‐Paper‐Scissors,
Brave Drum's penetrate ability
will come back into effect!
And that, combined with
Demon Lord, Gagnar's lifelink
will give Principal
Ikarino 5 damage points!
And we can go home!
So you think you
can beat me, do you?
Really, don't
make me laugh.
I wonder what he'll choose.
I think I'd go with paper.
Rock for me.
Scissors.
So our freedom depends
on a game of chance, huh?
Weird.
Yeah, right?
Rock, paper...
Scissors!
Scissors, for the win!
Engage, Rock Ram Bunker!
Go get him, Drum!
(screaming)
Game over.
Winner: Gao Mikado.
Let's go, this
detention's over, people.
(chatter)
Thank you, Gao, now we
can all get out of here.
Quite impressive.
Your students have promising
futures ahead of them.
As you know, they're
my pride and joy.
Great match, principal.
Okay, well, I'll leave
you to your students.
See you soon, Gnarly.
Stay out of trouble.
Weren't those two
fighting a second ago?
Yeah, grownups are
pretty strange, huh?
Yo, A‐Dawg, I gotta ask
you, are demons really bad?
Well, Tets, those
considered the most bad
are the ones whose
best friends are humans.
Really?
So, I guess I'm
as bad as they come.
Cool.
Okay, let's get back
to the classroom.
(yelling)
Whoa, awesome.
Principal, what's the big
idea, keeping me waiting, huh?
Neginoyama!
What are you doing?
Principal or not,
you can't just go around
making your entire
class disappear!
You took a student with
you from another class!
I'm sorry, let me explain!
I kind of wonder who
would win if those two
were in a Buddyfight
against each other.
Yeah.
So, what do you
think, is it possible?
The boy's even better
than we thought.
Leave him to me.
So it's all according to plan.
It's time for...
Tasuku and Gao's...
Card of the Day.
Today, we're going to introduce
you to my Buddy Jackknife's
new evolved form, it's
called Jackknife "Savior."
To call him, place
him on top of Jack.
He has Soulguard, plus
he gains the Move ability.
And, if you evolve him from
Jack when he already has a soul,
then the Soulguard
gets an increase too.
A secret weapon for
a Jack‐based deck.
So what do you think, guys?
Think you can open
up one of these?
You'll never know until you try!
♪
Next time, Terumi Kuchinawa
of Disaster tries to pull
a fast one on Gao,
but Tetsuya's rocking away
stop her in her tracks.
Next episode, Medusa Unleashed.
Join us for a Buddyfight.