♪
Do you have what it
takes to Buddyfight?
Choose your favorite world
and use special cards
to summon its powerful
monsters into reality.
Challenge other fighters
and buddy call your toughest
ally to fight by your side.
Get ready to
raise the flag!
Who's my next opponent?
Bravo! That
was wonderful.
Huh?
Very impressive, but tell
me, you're a smart guy.
You must have noticed
that I slipped that
card into your deck.
I only used it in
the name of justice!
Yes, that's right,
and fighting for justice
requires massive power and a
buddy to replace your Jack.
I'd be happy to give
you both of those things.
As a friend.
♪
I'd like you to
meet my buddy, Azi Dahaka.
Now, why don't
we begin our fight?
♪
What went down?
Tasuku!
♪
How could this
have happened?
Which one of you could
have done this to him?
♪
You're outmatched here, Gao.
I'm surprised you
beat the Grim Reaper.
Good will always
win over bad.
And I had such high
expectations for him.
(growls)
Looks like I missed
all the fun.
♪
Why don't you
allow me to clean up
this little mess
we have here?
(snickers)
Yes, go right ahead.
Why are you just
standing there?
Do your duty and escort
Master Kyoya to safety.
Really!
Yeah.
Hey, leave him alone!
♪
Now then.
I think it's
time to bring out
a few of my
newest friends.
(gasps)
No way!
It's Tsukikage!
Rise and shine.
It's time to earn your keep,
my beautiful puppets.
Take that!
(grunting)
Their abilities.
They're the ones from
their original worlds.
But I don't get it!
I thought monsters couldn't
use their powers on Earth.
Please!
Somebody get this
flying lizard off of me!
Look out!
(grunts)
Snap out of it,
Ninja Boy!
I thought you were supposed
to be Zanya's buddy.
Zanya.
Oh, not again.
Aren't you the
strong willed one?
I guess I'll need to turn
the heat up just a touch.
♪
Drum!
You were going to join the
Buddy Police together, remember?
♪
Nin.
I don't understand
why it's not working.
Fight it, don't
let it control you.
Please, you
must leave here.
Hang on.
You can talk?
I was so worried!
Are you okay?
Get ready.
I will create a diversion
for your escape.
What's going on?
♪
Hurry.
I don't know how much
longer I can do this.
I'm made of ice!
I can't possibly
taste that good!
Be a good little
monster and obey me,
or I'll have to find
another use for you.
(grunting)
Go on.
Get yourself
out of here.
I'll be okay.
No chance!
Cyber Ninja Arts.
Self‐Destruct,
Touch Me Not.
Nin!
Hey!
Tsukikage!
♪
Get out of here.
Go, now!
(shouts)
Future Force Armed.
(wind whistles)
Huh?
Wait, is that‐‐
(roaring)
Gao.
They need your help.
How could Roaring Slash
Gargantua Punisher
go off by itself, bro?
I know, but like I said, I don't
remember how it all went down.
All I know is that
Mr. Takihara was there
and he helped me get Kiri and
Drum to safety just in time.
I don't know.
Are you sure you didn't imagine
that part of the story?
Don't be like that.
I believe what
Gao is saying.
Anyway, how are
you Drum, you okay?
Oh, yeah, we dragons heal
faster than we shed skin.
Well, almost as fast.
So, what happened
to Kiri and Tasuku?
Kiri has to lay low and
rest up for a little while,
and I don't
know about Tasuku.
Those Disaster guys
took him somewhere!
♪
Wait a sec.
I think that's Tsukikage's
scarf, isn't it?
I'm so sorry, Zanya.
There was nothing
I could do.
It just happened.
Your buddy is‐‐
♪
No!
It has to be a lie!
Goodbye, old friend.
(energy charging)
It's a note
from Tsukikage!
He's okay!
Of course!
He's an immortal
nanomachine ninja!
That's why he's
a part of everything.
Sorry, I don't get it.
He's made up
of nanomachines.
Basically, machines
that are so small,
you can't see them
with the naked eye.
Each one is alive and even
when the parts are separated,
Tsukikage lives on.
None of that stuff
matters to me.
As long as he's
all right, I'm happy.
Yes, but most of him is
still in the enemy's grasp.
If we don't get him back,
he can't become the
Tsukikage he used to be.
Look, bro, the
words are changing.
Really?
(gasps)
Oh, deary me.
I wasn't quite ready
for my audience just yet.
Tsukikage!
By the look of his eyes,
he's not on our side.
I know.
He's under Kabala's
control again.
Tsukikage, don't you
recognize me?
My apologies.
He's not very sociable.
Why don't you just
leave him alone, huh?
Look, you're our teacher
and that's Zanya's buddy,
so then why aren't
you giving him back?
I should be asking
you that very thing.
As it stands now,
this monster is my buddy,
and I believe you kids
have one of his components.
You should return it.
♪
Not likely, huh?
Nin!
I guess it's no big
deal if I'm missing
just a miniscule
fragment like that,
but the thought of
you kids having it
is rather irksome to me.
On my planet, we've got
a word for guys like you.
It's loosely translated as
"North Beetle Droppings."
You're amusing.
Why don't we settle
this on the fighting stage?
What say maybe
today after school.
If Gao can defeat me,
I'll return everything.
Zanya's deck and
his defective ninja.
But just be warned
that if I win,
I'll be taking that
cute little chunk
of my buddy from you.
I am beautiful!
Nothing, really?
You kids need
to get out more.
What's next?
Are you gonna start crying
for your mommies now?
Ooh, the teacher
took my card.
You can't let
him get to you, man.
Tsukikage's being controlled
somehow, but don't worry.
I'll get him back.
You really think
you can win?
Why not?
I don't know.
If Tsukikage is his buddy,
he's probably
going to use my deck.
I guess what I'm saying is
that I doubt you could beat it.
Come on, Z!
Don't you want
Gao to win?
I didn't ask him
for his help.
And I didn't ask
for this match!
But I stand by my friends.
We all need to
work together.
♪
Huh?
You really want to
join me in the fight?
Nin!
Be careful.
Do what you want, but I
won't give you any advice.
I'll just observe
the match from here.
Good to have the
old Zanya back.
Do you mind if mini‐Tsukikage
joins the fun?
Do what you want.
So, we can finally begin.
Sword of beauty,
pierce the darkness
and destroy
this silly boy!
Luminize!
Kisaragi Ninja Arts
Side Story!
I knew it, he's
using my deck.
The most powerful
deck of all!
Blazing a path
toward the future!
Luminize!
Explosive Dragon Fang!
Another new deck?
This is one fight
we can't afford to lose.
So I made sure Gao
had all the right cards.
You'll never guess
how he got the name.
Baku thought of explosive.
Dragon is for Drum, and Fang
is for Gao's sharp attacks.
Together, they're
Explosive Dragon Fang!
You went to great lengths
this time, didn't you?
It reeks of desperation.
‐Time to raise the flag!
I fight for Dragon World!
I fight for Katana World.
Is it all right if
I have the first move?
Yeah.
Always so courteous,
even now.
Oh, you really
are a shining example.
I think I'll save this
handsome card for later.
I charge and I draw.
I call to the center,
Accelerate Ninja, Hayate!
Rise, my lovely, and attack
little Gao with all your might!
♪
(grunts)
End of move.
(sighs)
We've got some
questions, Kabala,
and we deserve
to know the truth.
Oh, it's no secret.
I use wrinkle cream to
stay looking so young.
Are you the one who's
controlling Tsukikage?
Who else would it be?
I do it with this mind
suppressor I installed
on my Dark Core Deck case.
Oh, dear, now I'm
saying too much.
(giggling)
Right, Baku, it's
time I witnessed
your deck building
skills in action.
♪
Now it's my turn.
I buddy call
Drum to the right.
The buddy gift
gives me one life point.
Then I call Thousand Rapier
Dragon to the left.
And I equip Steel Fist,
Dragoknuckle!
I see you've set him up
to use the Gao Formation.
Yeah, no flies on you.
It's sweet cause
with two monsters,
plus himself,
he gets three attacks.
Okay, Thousand,
attack Hayate!
Yes, sir.
♪
(grunting)
Adieu!
Okay, Drum, you
attack the fighter!
No sweat!
(grunts)
♪
Crash Drill
Rad Bunker!
♪
Steel Fist!
I cast the Beautiful
Art of Item Blasting!
Uh‐oh.
(grunts)
End of move.
That was Big Z's card.
The Ninja Arts spell destroys
items on the field.
The first objective
in any match
is to prevent the opponent
from doing what they want,
and then when you've managed
to gain the upper hand,
victory is sure to follow.
How could you do
something like to my buddy?
It was quite easy, actually,
and what would you have me do?
I can't just let
a dangerous monster
storm around doing
whatever it wants.
What?
Monsters aren't able
to use their powers
when they're
in our world.
He wasn't dangerous at all.
Yeah, hate to tell you,
but that's not really true.
What?
Your friend's right.
We found a way
to allow monsters
to use their true power
and knowing this,
I'm sure you'd agree
that it's necessary
to be able
to control them.
So, Tsukikage is some
experimental subject?
I suppose he is.
It's just 'til we've
worked out all the kinks.
I call to the right,
Stealth Ninja Kirikakure Saizo.
I also call Hayate
to the left area again.
And I buddy call to the center,
Nanomachine Ninja Tsukikage!
Now, obey me, my powerful
mind controlled puppets
and attack the fighter!
♪
(grunts)
‐Gao!
‐That's intense.
End of move.
I'm so bored.
When you said you'd
be using a new deck,
I was expecting
great things.
I fought grannies
who are better than you.
The basic strategy
of Buddyfighting
is clearing a
path to the fighter.
Once the center
position is open,
you're free to
deal him damage.
All decks should
be built with cards
that can destroy an
opponent's center monster
and with cards that
can protect your center.
To win, one must be
patient and calculated.
That was fast!
Gao only has two
life points left.
Kabala took advantage of his
formation's lack of defense.
But that's the core
of his fighting style,
and why Explosive
Dragon Fang exists.
Yeah, I know.
The deck isn't about
off setting weaknesses.
It's about boosting
the strengths.
It's a deck I built so that Gao
could do whatever he wants.
Explosive Dragon Fang is for
soaring to the highest point.
Now, things are
gonna get serious.
Draw!
(growls)
(grunts)
Charge and draw!
I call Boomerang Dragon
to the center position!
Let me at 'em,
let me at 'em.
That's it!
The card that can turn
things around for us!
What's a Size Zero monster
from Dragon World going to do?
I'm not done yet!
I equip my Dragon
Blade Drum's sword.
Cornered like a scared rat.
Why else would he give up on
his Gao Formation technique
and shift to
protecting his center?
The kid definitely has
a gift for improvising!
Thousand, attack
Tsukikage in the center!
‐Yes, sir!
‐No, not him!
Impero Veritas!
Body Replacement!
♪
Drum, attack him again!
It's useless.
I'll just continue
discarding non‐monster cards
and he'll keep coming back.
Nanomachine
Body Replacement.
Yeah, but now you've used up
all the cards in your hand.
Say it's not so.
Then I guess poor Tsukikage
will be destroyed
in your next attack.
No matter, it's the last
one you'll be able to make.
When you equipped that
big sword back there,
you sacrificed
valuable life points,
and failed to clear
the monster from my center,
which means, you
can't attack me.
I wouldn't be so
sure about that.
Get a load of the
evolved Gao Formation!
Let's go!
Let fly, Boomerang Dragon!
I'm going off like
a frog in a sock!
(grunting)
Oh, no!
You wouldn't want to
meet me in the Outback.
See what I did there, mate?
Watch out,
I'm coming back at ya!
It's returning to
the cards in his hand?
As we know, after the card
goes back to the hand,
it's possible to
attack using an item.
It'll be a quadruple attack.
And don't forget, you guys,
when a monster returns
to the hand or deck,
the Drum sword gains
one extra critical point.
‐Oh, yeah!
‐Check this out.
The next generation
Gao Formation!
(grunts, screams)
(Kabala laughing)
Love it!
What a wonderful
display, Mikado!
Say, would you consider
joining our team?
In your dreams.
I can't be friends
with people
who think it's okay to use
machines to control buddies.
Don't be naive.
What's the harm in
removing unpredictability?
All we seek is to
create a simple world
where everything is
completely under control.
If you ask me, mathematically,
it's beautiful!
How do you figure?
Mathematics is
precise and exact.
An aesthetic pursuit
that delivers beauty.
When searching
for a solution,
you follow the
simplest path possible,
and you're always left
with the most elegant way
to solve the problem.
I guess I kind of
see what you mean.
You do?
And anything
aside from logic,
for example, the bond between
a fighter and his buddy,
all that should be erased
according to you, huh?
Yes, when rounding off
to the nearest decimal,
some things just
don't make the cut.
Then you're saying
that you would get rid
of a monster's free will and
spirit just so he'd obey you?
I like kids who are
quick to understand.
Tell me, Zanya,
would you be interested
in joining our
little team?
Huh!
Let me ask you
something.
Do you know why Tsukikage
chooses to be silent?
Do tell.
It's not that
he can't talk.
He's just made a conscious
decision not to speak.
By committing to
a vow of silence,
he strengthens his will
and his inner spirit.
That's why he was
the only buddy
who couldn't be
fully controlled.
I can't believe that sneaky
ninja's been holding out on us!
Even now as he stands there
his training continues.
Which would mean that Tsukikage
hasn't lost his spirit at all,
wouldn't you agree?
Is there a point
in there somewhere?
Oh, there's
a point alright.
Your device didn't remove his
will, it just suppressed it.
And just barely by
the looks of it.
Consider this.
What do you think
would happen
if a smaller group
of his nanomachines,
that clearly had
its own free will,
reconnected with him?
You mean, like
that mini thingy?
(gasps)
Where did that
little nuisance go?
♪
Please don't hurt me!
It took you long
enough to notice!
Nin.
I designed the mind
suppression program myself.
This can't be happening!
Error.
I guess this
proves one thing.
That the bond between Zanya and
Tsukikage trumps your machines.
Those calculations were wrong.
Hey, take that back!
You don't know
what you're saying.
Did anyone notice that
my turn isn't over yet?
I cast Dragonic Charge!
♪
He just increased
his gauge by two points.
You've got five, and
Kabala has less than five,
and neither of them has a
monster in the center area.
That's it, bro!
Blow him away!
It's time for
the Final Phase!
♪
Nice deck.
I cast!
Remember, Baku, a deck
is a means to winning,
and you have to use whatever
means are necessary.
You've clearly become
a great deck builder,
but you have yet to come up
against one built by me.
♪
Impact!
Roaring Slash!
Gargantua Punisher!
♪
Oh, this isn't good!
(roaring)
♪
Game over.
Winner: Gao Mikado.
Oh, yeah, that's how
you take back control.
Even cards that usually
dominate against normal decks
are useless against
the awesome power
of the Darkness
Dragon World.
The enemy cannot benefit from
their unique fighting style,
which prevents them from
achieving their full potential.
This world has
many advantages.
First, there's
Shadow Dive.
An ability that
allows a monster
to bypass the opponent's
center monster
and cause direct
damage to the fighter.
Next is Spectral Strike.
After destroying a monster,
it also applies
damage to the fighter,
but unlike Penetrate,
it can be used
on the right and
left monsters too.
♪
Observe your opponent,
predict their next move,
then turn the
tables on them.
Baku, the power of Darkness
Dragon World will guide you
as it shatters the
dreams of the defeated.
Once reunited,
we will celebrate
our victory together.
As promised.
You better not be
playing a trick on me.
Just be thankful you
got your buddy back!
If there's nothing else,
toodles!
Not so fast, we still
have a few more questions.
I kept my promise, Mikado.
You're on your
own for the rest.
Tell us, or we'll go
talk to the Buddy Police.
Well, you go
right ahead then.
But they won't
listen to you kids.
(gasping)
What is it that you
think they'll do to me?
Sadly, the adult world
isn't quite as understanding
as your innocent little
brains think it is.
What are you
trying to say?
I'll leave you with this.
Think of it as a
special gift from me.
I'm just way
too nice, I guess.
Take it!
♪
Have a look.
Yes, it's for
the Gaen Cup!
A Buddyfight tournament that
will be announced very soon.
Hey, where'd he
disappear to?
♪
If you enter and compete,
you might just find some of
the answers you're looking for.
Like where your
friend Tasuku was taken.
♪
Crazy, huh?
I will find him.
It's time for...
Tasuku and Gao's...
‐Card of the day!
Today, we're
gonna talk about
the super cool
Boomerang Dragon card.
From the Explosive
Dragon Fang deck.
It has the ability of
returning to the cards
in the hand
after it attacks.
So then you can totally call
him to the center, repeat...
And the center
monster will disappear,
so you'll be able to attack
again using your equipped item.
That means you'd be able to do
a quadruple attack every turn!
So, what do
you think, guys?
You think you can
open up one of these?
You'll never know
until you try!
♪
Next time, determined to expose
the Gaen Cup for what it is,
Zanya decides to compete.
Gao isn't so sure
it's the right choice,
but Tetsuya's
more than game.
Next episode,
"Balle du Soleil Reborn!"
Join us for
a Buddyfight!