Do you have what it
takes to Buddyfight?
Choose your favorite world
and use special cards
to summon its powerful
monsters into reality.
Challenge other fighters,
and Buddy Call your
toughest ally to fight
by your side.
Get ready to
raise the flag.
(wind blowing)
♪
As you know,
unlike previous rounds,
the fight pairings
for today's final
have been selected for us.
They are as follows:
Gao against Tasuku.
Zanya will be
fighting Rouga.
And Tetsuya will be
facing our school's
former vice president, Sofia.
Lucky for us, we
have a lot of Tasuku
and Rouga's matches on video.
So you two should
look at them
and familiarize
yourselves with
their fighting styles.
‐Good idea.
‐I'll memorize them all!
Hmm.
Our only unknown is Sofia.
‐Mm‐hmm, mm‐hmm.
I'm afraid we don't
have much data on her.
Until now, she's never
actually participated
in an official fight.
Yeah, bro.
So Kuguru and I
are gonna recreate
the entire fight she
had against Kanahebi.
Sounds fly.
Can I do a cameo?
We got time to get
some popcorn so we can
get our snack on
while we watch?
‐Time to raise the flag.
I'm with Katana World.
I fight for Legend World.
The first thing
Sofia did was
charge and draw.
And then she said...
"I call Sirius
Lailaps to the center.
Now, go attack the fighter."
(grunts)
He used his set spell
Dark Ninja Technique,
Poison Mist Formation
to reduce Sofia's life points
on each turn.
Then played final showdown
on the Great Gojo Bridge.
With this spell card,
neither player can attack
monsters in the
right or left areas.
And with the Fire
Streak Ninja, Gokuen
in the center, he can
increase his defense
if he discards
the ninja cards
in his hand.
If I was Sofia right now,
I'd be shaking in
my high tops thinking,
"How am I gonna
attack this guy?"
You're telling me, Tuke.
I attack Lailaps
using Gokuen.
And I open up your
center and inflict
two damage using
Yoichi and Yamigarasu.
This is where Sofia's
skill really shines.
I call to the left
Moon Celestial, Selene.
To the center
Sirius Lailaps,
and I Buddy Call
to the right
Stellar Deity, Astraeus.
A Buddy Gift gives me
back one life point,
and since I'm on a roll,
I'll set a spell.
Great Fate, Frozen Stars.
♪
Harsh, bro.
Great Fate, Frozen Stars
is very useful 'cause it
disables all the abilities
of the opponent's card
when there are star
attribute monsters
in the right and
left positions.
(Baku groans)
I can't power up my cards.
Kanahebi's combo
took a nose‐dive, yo.
Selene, Lailaps,
attack the fighter.
(groans)
♪
It's clear that
Kanahebi's challenge here
was to neutralize
Freezing Stars, but‐‐
With Astraeus
in the field,
the Star Monsters
on the left and right
can't be destroyed.
That's my jam.
It's like a reverse
Great Gojo Bridge.
Mm‐hmm.
I call to the center
Electron Ninja, Shiden.
I've no choice but
to attack her center.
♪
Hmm.
I've got you just
where I want you.
I call Rigel Orion
to the center area,
allowing me to
get to the point.
I attack Shiden with
Star Bow, Artemis Arrow.
♪
Selene, Orion,
and Astraeus,
go and attack
the fighter, now!
♪
(groans)
(laughs)
You'll do better
next time, Baku.
You forget that I'm not
the one who got defeated.
And, for the record,
you're not Sofia,
and she doesn't laugh
anything like that, you know?
(airy laugh)
The Gaen Cup began
with eight specially
chosen teams, and tonight
one of the last two will
be crowned champions.
Will it be Team Purgatory
or Team Balle du Soleil?
The final round
is about to begin!
My guess is that
Sofia's deck will
probably look
something like this.
Thanks a mill, Baku.
This'll help a lot.
There's a strong chance
that she'll change up
her deck for the final round.
But I kinda doubt her
basic fighting style
will alter that much.
A style that doesn't let
opponent's do anything.
I thought of that.
The key to the game
will be this:
Great Fate, Frozen Stars.
That's the one all right.
Okay, guys.
I made us lunch.
Why don't you
take a little break?
Did she say a break?
No way, man.
We haven't even caught
half of Tasuku's fights yet.
We don't have
time for a break!
(groans)
You guys sure about that?
'Cause right now
you're kinda scaring us.
Although it's essential
to do research on your
opponent before a match,
it's even more important
to go onto the stage
with your body and
mind in tip top shape.
Kuguru's epic feast took
care of the body part,
now just try and relax
and let your mind
forget about
things for a while.
(Gao scoffs)
How could I forget
about Buddyfighting?
'Sup, dudes?
Gao, how's it going?
Huh?
That's your plan?
Bringing us to Castle?
Are you kidding me?
(groans)
I hope your idea works.
Huh?
Hey, isn't
that Gao Mikado?
Yeah, look,
it's really him.
(laughing)
‐Hey, wanna Buddyfight?
‐Me too!
‐Me next.
‐Don't forget about me!
(giggling)
Sure!
I'll take you all on.
It's the best way to
take his mind off things.
Yeah, when you're doing
something you love,
you don't have
to think at all.
My body and mind are one.
Meditation is the best
way to clear one's mind
of stress and distractions.
This way, please.
Hmm?
(groans)
No, you gotta leave!
Big Z can't have
girls near him!
Huh?
(giggling)
Girls!
Shimmy left, right.
Put on the hat,
stayin' alive,
and pose.
You were totally
tearing it up, Tets.
Dancing really is the
best way to recharge, A‐Dawg.
But it's kinda weird, you know?
I'm not used to busting
out my sick moves without
a crowd gathering
to cheer me on.
There's a reason
no one's come around.
A certain someone's been
working behind the scenes
to keep everyone away.
Isn't that right,
former vice president?
Sofia?
What?
I know you Disaster
guys are a little
over the top,
but come on, girlfriend,
stalking?
You here to scope
out my mad skills?
I came to tell you
to forfeit today's fight.
Forfeit?
That's totally whack.
In today's final round,
the only contest
that Master Kyoya
cares about is the one
between Gao Mikado
and Tasuku Ryuenji.
The other two don't matter.
Huh?
I don't like doing
meaningless things.
So, I think you
should forfeit.
It may be
meaningless for you,
but it means
something to us!
You hear me?
Why don't you be
the one to forfeit?
Master Kyoya and everyone
else knows that your friend
here has no chance.
My power's unmatched.
You may be sure
of victory,
but you know
as well as us
that the Buddyfight
stage has witnessed
its share of upsets.
(chuckle)
Would information about
that girl change your mind?
What girl?
The one that
Master Kyoya named
Terumi Kuchinawa.
Huh?
But I'm gonna call
the Power of Love here.
♪
All right!
Do I know you?
(groans)
Are you saying you
really know who she is?
Yes.
You're the one who
erased her memories,
aren't you?
Maybe.
Huh?
(groans)
Why would you do something
so mean to her, huh?
She was unable to
fulfill her mission
and was dismissed
from her duties
within Disaster.
It had to be done in order
to protect our secrets.
(groans)
(chuckles)
She's lucky that nothing
worse happened to her.
Huh?
Even if you fight
the fight of your life,
you'll never beat me.
Let's hope for your sake you
make the intelligent decision.
♪
Tetsuya.
Welcome back.
As you can see,
it's a beautiful
clear evening here tonight,
and the stars are
shining brightly
both in the sky and here
on the Buddyfight stage.
The stadium is electric
with excitement as the first
game of the final round
is about to begin between
Sofia Sakharov
from Team Purgatory
and Tetsuya Kurodake
from Team Balle du Soleil.
This is the first
time we're seeing
these two face off.
What's gonna happen?
You're foolish.
I can't believe
that you just
ignored my advice.
I'm gonna make you regret it.
Midnight sky,
stop the earth
where it spins, and
freeze history solid.
Dark Luminize,
Winter Diamond!
The night we've
been waiting for.
And have you
done as I asked?
(chuckles)
They won't know
what hit them.
♪
‐Time to raise the flag.
I fight with Magic World.
I fight for Legend World.
♪
Sofia will go first.
I charge and draw.
Sofia has called
Rigel Orion to the center.
That lets her discard
up to two star attribute
cards from her hand,
and then draw the same
number of cards.
I knew it, she's going
for that combo, bro.
Go Orion, and
attack the fighter.
♪
End of move.
Ugh...
Come on, Tets, let's
get this show rolling.
Huh?
I'm on it, yo.
Check it!
Draw.
Charge and draw.
I call Great Duke,
Astaroth to the center.
And pull one of the 72
Pillars cards from my hand
into his soul.
Good.
And to cramp your style,
I'll cast Nice One!
With that spell, Tetsuya
can draw two cards!
And a set spell.
Solomon's Great Barrier.
I know this one.
All of the size two 72
Pillars Magic World monsters
become size one.
Impressive.
I call Sky Poet,
Amon to the right,
and Fallen Angel
of Rage, Beleth
to the left.
It's a lineup
of size two monsters!
Time to say goodbye.
Astaroth has
destroyed Rigel Orion.
And now he's coming
in for a double attack.
Someone call
for an encore?
Order from disorder springs.
♪
Finally, I can
be of some use!
Hardly.
I cast Holy Grail.
Aw, you've gotta
be kidding me.
End of move.
Sofia staved off
Beleth's attack
with a counter spell,
but her life points
have been cut down to five.
Still, she doesn't
seem concerned at all.
If she's able to set up
the Freezing Stars
and Astraeus combo,
then his Magic World deck
would be at a huge
disadvantage.
He needs to take as many
life points off her
as he can before that happens.
Way to go, Tetsuya.
You're doing awesome, man!
Yeah, so far
so good, bro.
See, I told you there was
no need for you to worry.
It's weird, though.
I mean, he hasn't
danced once yet.
Hey, you're right.
He still has some time.
Stars, guide me.
Sofia's called three
monsters at the same time.
And one of them is
her Buddy Monster,
Stellar Deity, Astraeus.
Thanks to her Buddy Gift,
she regains
one life point.
Here's my set spell.
It's called Great
Fate, Frozen Stars.
All your cards freeze.
♪
And you'll find you
can't make a single move.
♪
I was wondering
when I'd see it.
That spell is incredible.
It nullifies all of
the abilities of your
opponent's cards.
The effect of Solomon's Great
Barrier has been nullified,
and Tetsuya must now
send two of his monsters
in the field to
the drop zone
for being oversized.
Amon, Beleth, my crew.
I'm sorry.
Farewell, sire.
I never get
to hit anyone.
How unfair!
Great Fate also
prevents Astaroth
from using his
soulguard ability.
Now, I cast Symbel Gard.
♪
And attack Astaroth
with Astraeus.
I have no regrets.
No, Astaroth!
(groans)
End of move.
It's your turn, Tets.
Come on, we still
have a chance.
Hey, get up, now!
The thing is, A‐Dawg...
I wanna know more
about that girl.
♪
I wanna know
her real name,
her birth date,
her interests,
her favorite
kind of music.
♪
Would it be okay
if I forfeit now?
♪
Can you hear what
he's saying out there?
No, the little
bro's mumbling.
I just wanna see her again.
Right down to
the smallest thing.
I wanna tell her what she's
forgotten about herself.
Even, like, what she
ate for breakfast
the Tuesday before.
I see.
Hey, Sofia what's‐her‐face!
Huh?
Try this on for size!
What?
(moans)
(laughs)
That's a great look for you.
Goin' a little
bananas, are we?
That's enough!
♪
Hold the phone, it's
the same amazing power
that Rouga Aragami
demonstrated for us
in his fight
against Kirisame.
Makes sense now
that I think about it.
Sofia does use a
Dark Core Deck Case.
Emergency.
♪
I'm freezing!
Since the field
has frozen over,
we're gonna have
to put the fight
on ice for a
little while, guys.
We thank you in advance
for your understanding.
You certainly don't
see that every day.
Sofia never gets riled up
by an opponent's taunts.
At times she can lack
some self‐restraint.
I've been unsuccessful
at getting her to understand
how losing your composure
works against you.
(ice breaks)
Whoa.
Look up there, Tets.
Huh?
Can you see, in the balcony?
It's her.
♪
Thanks for your
patience, everyone.
The fight will
now resume.
So, what do you wanna do?
♪
Hey...
maybe...
do you think she
came to watch me fight?
I don't know.
But you're gonna have
to make up your mind.
The clock is ticking and
the crowd's getting antsy.
Just think, though.
If she knew you got
info about her because
you forfeited the fight,
would she be
cool with that?
Let's see how Tetsuya
responds on his turn.
He calls Sky Poet, Amon
to the right, and Buddy Calls
Demon Lord, Asmodai
to the center.
(growling)
Demon Drop Kick!
Amon is attacking Sofia.
I cast...
Starfall Night.
Now all the size one or
smaller star attribute monsters
in her drop zone
are free to come out.
Procyon Melampus.
♪
Forgive me.
I've no choice
but to destroy you.
Hah!
End of move.
Focus.
She's the one who
stole the girl
you like's memories.
Hmm.
I call to the center
Procyon Melampus,
and equip Star Bow,
Artemis Arrow.
♪
Asking for favors from someone
who picks on your friends.
Are you really
okay with that?
'Cause I'm not!
(groans)
Silence, you measly monster.
Don't do it!
No, A‐Dawg!
Tetsuya's all
alone out there now.
(shouts)
I wish there was something
we could do to help.
With Great Fate, Frozen
Stars doing its thing,
it's nearly impossible for
Tetsuya to turn this around.
Come on, man.
Mic check, mic check,
one two, one two.
It's show time!
(music blares)
When I'm dancing to my jam,
everybody knows who I am.
Tetsuya has just
launched into a routine.
Does this mean he's
given up on winning?
One, two.
Look, he's smiling.
Yeah, he's acting
like himself again.
Everyone.
Core Gadgets
is in the move,
but that's not
way cool smooth.
So I say, come on,
let's groove!
Tetsuya just
increased his gauge
with Key of Solomon,
First Volume.
I cast Great Spell,
Devil's Rock and Roll.
Homie should've
started dancing sooner.
That spell returns
all monsters
to the player's hands.
I see what he's
trying to do.
Let's just hope it
gives him enough time
for it to work.
What a move!
By sending Sofia's
units back to her hand,
Great Fate's
ability has nullified
and the freeze is undone.
Plus, Tetsuya's
Solomon's Great Barrier
is reactivated.
What's more is that Devil's
Rock and Roll's ability
lets Tetsuya call as many
72 Pillars monsters as he wants
from the top five
cards in his deck.
Demon Sommelier, Zagan.
Yo, yo, yo.
Fallen Angel of Rage, Beleth.
Yo, yo, yo, let me
hit 'em this time, yo.
And my favorite homeboy and
buddy, Demon Lord, Asmodai.
In the house.
Hey, A‐Dawg, here's
something I just remembered.
Hm?
What I really want
that girl to know
isn't her history or info,
I wanna tell her how
fun Buddyfighting is, yo.
A'ight.
Now, let's get
back to biz.
It's a mass attack
by the 72 Pillars army.
I have something for you.
This time I won't miss.
♪
Here's the finish.
You haven't seen
the last of me!
Game over.
Winner: Tetsuya Kurodake.
We rockin' the bananas
and soon'll be chillin'
in our pajamas.
We rockin' the bananas
and soon'll be chillin'
in our pajamas.
I didn't think
it was possible
for her to lose.
Many gifts are found
in the unexpected.
(chuckles)
(groans)
Hmm?
What are you doing?
What if someone saw
you using those powers?
I guess I'd just
erase their memory.
Even you get
frustrated when you lose.
You killed it out there, man!
You talking about his
cardfighting or his dancing?
Okay, we're up next.
So, are you ready?
Nin.
(panting)
Hey.
Remember me?
Why, of course
I do, Tetsu dear.
Ugh, what?
You're one of
Asmodai's doubles?
What's the matter?
All I said was that
you should look up
in the balcony.
I never told you
that Terumi was
actually here, did I?
You're supposed to
be my homie, A‐Dawg.
What did you expect?
I am a demon.
Hmm.
I guess it's what
I needed to win.
Thanks, yo.
Hey, it was easy,
just like magic.
(giggles)
All right.
Let's give 'em
a victory dance.
Yo, yo.
Buddyfights sure look
like they'd be a lot of fun.
‐‐our pajamas.
Don't let our
dance moves fool ya.
On the Buddyfight stage,
we'll school you, yo.
Word!
It's time for‐‐
Tasuku and Gao's‐‐
Card of the Day!
Today we're gonna
tell you all about
the amazing card
Great Fate, Frozen Stars.
If you use it and have
star attribute cards
in your left
and right position,
you can nullify
the abilities
of all the cards
in your opponent's
field and soul.
And if you have
Stellar Deity, Astraeus
in play, then the star
attribute cards in your
left and right area
can't be destroyed.
It's a tough combo
that's sure to give
your opponent
a big surprise.
So, what do you think, guys?
You think you can
open up one of these?
You'll never know
until you try!
♪
Next time...
we all know Rouga's been
living in Kyoya's shadow,
but in the middle of
his fight against Zanya,
he surprises us all
and does something
only a true friend would do.
Next episode:
Rouga Leaves the Pack!
Join us for a Buddyfight!