Do you have what it
takes to Buddyfight?
Choose your favorite world
and use special cards
to summon its powerful
monsters into reality.
Challenge other fighters,
and Buddy Call your toughest
ally to fight by your side.
Get ready to raise the flag!
(crying)
My Tsukikage, he's gone forever.
Don't say that!
We'll get him back.
I'm sure we will.
If anybody stood a chance
against the Grim Reaper,
Zanya did.
Now it's official‐‐
I'm hungry and I'm mad!
I don't get it!
Why did he have to go
and do something so unfair?
I could be wrong, but it
sounds like you know who he is.
You feel like sharing?
If you know something
that'll help us,
you better spit it out!
Well, I...
♪
Gao, you could never understand
what it was like for me.
There's no friend of mine
who would ever do this
to another Buddyfighter!
Don't worry, big brother.
We'll find out who he is.
‐I'll help, too.
‐Leave him alone!
You had your chance,
I'm taking him home!
I can't imagine.
Come on, we gotta go.
♪
Losing your buddy
must be harsh, bro.
There's gotta be
something we can do.
‐It's my fault.
‐Why?
I should've been the one
fighting the Grim Reaper.
And I should be the one
putting a stop to this,
so I will.
♪
We've finally found you,
Vice President Sakharov.
‐Former Vice President.
‐I stand corrected.
I keep forgetting that
she transferred schools.
Anyway, that was
some pretty crafty work
tracking her down, Yamigitsune.
Have you got what
you promised me?
I'll give you your reward later.
Forget about that.
Aren't you the least bit
curious what she's doing here
at the Photon Metal Mine?
♪
(explosion)
(whimpering)
Really, I'd expect
more from someone
who's already come
back from the dead.
Getting any closer would
be far too dangerous now.
I assume you've
heard the rumors.
Our boy's famous.
We better not keep him waiting.
Hmm.
♪
Huh?
Nope, still not right!
Now there's too
much sugar in it!
Stella, are you okay?
Why aren't you at your station?
‐What's going on?
‐Tasuku!
Examiner Shido's made a
few changes around here.
Are you lost?
You have a lot of nerve
barging in without permission!
Commander I,
what are you doing
about this rogue Buddyfighter?
Why isn't your
team investigating?
Due to repeated use of
Buddy Police resources
for his own personal reasons,
Commander I was relieved
of his duties at this office.
You are now addressing
Commander Nobari.
Well, then, Commander‐‐
(tsking)
"Commander, sir."
There's a fighter out
there stealing buddies
in Core deck cases.
You need to defend
everyone from this criminal!
I think you're
confusing a threat
with silly, childish behavior!
"Hey, that's my toy!
Give it back right now!"
"Stop being such a crybaby,
I'm just gonna borrow it!"
(crying)
We have better things to do
than intervene in
children's squabbles.
But the Grim Reaper is using
one of those Dark
Core deck cases!
The same kind that Wolf
and Shosetsu Kirisame had?
If that's true, we'll be sure
to do a thorough investigation.
You can see yourself
out, good Samaritan.
I know I could help if
you gave me back my deck!
No way that's happening.
If you want to Buddyfight,
you better go buy
some cards at the store.
Can you open a Buddy Rare card?
Well played!
Thank you for your hard work.
Just sit tight, we'll need
to proceed carefully on this.
Huh?
So you want us to
just wait around?
Aren't you going to
come and arrest them?
I'm telling you,
they're up here
and their secret
hideout's not far.
I know, but we don't
wanna scare them off.
‐Whatever.
‐Huh?
Hey, wait, I can
call back later.
If you found the
enemy's hideout,
you need to get
out there right away!
We still don't have
enough proof yet.
But Gao and his
friends all saw him.
They're witnesses!
I get it, it's because
they're kids, right?
So their testimony
doesn't qualify.
I'm sorry, but our society
has these rules in place
for a reason, my friend.
Well, they're not right.
Those guys using the Dark Core
deck cases must be stopped!
Perhaps he senses the truth.
‐Commander?
‐Shh!
Who are you talking about?
I've been a janitor here
for the past 20 years!
Yes, of course.
Maybe it would be better if
we just told him the truth.
That our enemy
is powerful enough
to influence the operation of
the Buddy Police Department?
I don't think that he's
quite ready to hear that.
Hey, I know you!
You're Gao's friend, am I right?
Uh, yes, I'm Kazane Fujimiya.
‐Hi!
‐You here on police business?
Kinda‐‐Kem‐Kem‐‐uh, my
friend Kemura told me that...
Time for final phase!
(screaming)
This is my real deck.
You're kidding‐‐
Shido was really using
‐a Dark Core deck case?
‐That's not all.
Kem‐Kem also said
that he was fighting
for Darkness Dragon World.
That's it!
There's no way that
Examiner Sueroku
wouldn't know what
deck his son is using.
This can only mean
the Buddy Police
is already under
the enemy's control.
Really‐‐what'll happen next?
I only got into Buddyfighting
'cause it was so much fun,
but now those Dark Core thingies
are making it hard
to stay positive.
Don't worry, you leave
all of that up to me now.
Hmm.
Even if I'm all alone, I'll
never stop doing what's right.
Goodbye, Buddy Police.
♪
Did you find what
you're looking for?
Do you have some business
with Student Council
President Shido?
Or maybe you're here
to make an appointment!
‐Who are you?
‐Ouch, that hurts!
You mean you really
don't know who I am?
I know you!
And without your power,
you're really not
that scary, are you?
What‐‐you mean you know
about the Future Force?
Future?
We prefer to call it
Disaster Force, boy wonder.
You call it "Disaster"?
Perhaps you'd like a
little demonstration.
♪
Working late, I see!
How admirable.
Oh, what have we here?
Is everything all right?
Why is Mr. Ryuenji
at our school?
I was just asking
him the same thing.
It seems he's lost his way!
Maybe you can try and guide him.
You know, set him
on the right path.
(chuckling)
I didn't mean to cause trouble.
Are you sure you know
what you're doing?
Yes, someone has
to stop the Reaper
from taking people's buddies
and round up the others who
are controlling his actions.
It sounds like
your mind's made up.
I'd like you to take this.
♪
I've seen that before!
I know who that belongs to!
‐That must mean...
‐Shh!
Go to the Fuji
Photon Metal Mine.
Look for an abandoned shaft,
that is where you'll
find your answers.
Makes sense.
I didn't think they'd
be hiding underground.
That explains why
I haven't been able
to detect their presence!
♪
‐I won't let you down, sir!
‐One last thing.
I am just loaning
that to you, you know.
Please promise that you'll
return it in one piece!
Hmm.
♪
It is done, now I will
leave the rest up to you.
Hi, is Gao here?
Ahh!
‐Am I dreaming?
‐Hey, Tasuku!
How's it going, man?
‐Hey!
‐Hey, Gao!
Is she okay?
I dropped by 'cause
it's been a while
since our last Buddyfight.
I was hoping you'd accept
a friendly challenge.
You're kidding, right?
First tell me what's going on.
I know you didn't
come here just for that!
If you're challenging
me, there's a reason!
Does this have anything
to do with the Reaper?
Huh‐‐wait, let me guess.
He took your buddy,
and now you've decided
to stop Buddyfighting
like Zanya?
Huh?
(whining)
Not exactly, but I
did lose my buddy.
I'm going after the Reaper
and the Dark Core cases.
And hopefully reveal the mystery
of this Darkness Dragon World.
All right, then count us in!
Thing is we're not
gonna have any help
from the Buddy Police,
so there's a chance
it could get dangerous.
Yeah, and?
None of that's gonna stop me
from going with ya, you know.
Maybe I don't have the
same training or skills
as a Buddy Police officer,
but really, the thing is,
I'd never let any pal of mine
head into danger all by himself!
Wow, thank you.
You're a real friend.
Huh.
Hi, kids‐‐hey, aren't you
that famous boy wonder?
Get this, Gao and
Tasuku are taking off
to go and track down
some super bad guys!
No, it's like...man.
Hello, you must be Gao's father.
I've come here to ask your
son to help me right a wrong.
Yeah, that's it!
You think that my son
can be of help to you?
I do.
Okay then.
I can't see any
reason why he shouldn't.
It's important to
support your friends‐‐
am I right, Mighty Sun Fighter?
Thanks, Dad!
All right!
Give me your skimboard‐‐
come on, Drum!
It's not a skimboard,
it's a Buddy Skill!
Hmm.
Buddy Skill: On.
♪
You coming or not?
‐Hop on!
‐Cool!
♪
Go get 'em, guys!
You can do it!
(laughing)
Yup, he's definitely his
mother's son all right.
Without a doubt.
(wind blowing)
Wait, so you're saying
that these guys have taken
over the Buddy Police?
Yeah‐‐it's hard to believe,
but they're somehow connected.
We can't know who to trust.
We need to find them
before it's too late.
I still can't get my head
around Jack being all sealed up
and basically held prisoner.
It's just so cruel!
Without Jack's buddy skill,
how were you planning
on getting all the
way to Fuji Mine?
I mean, if I turned you down
and had to do
homework or something?
‐Uhh.
‐See that?
Without us awesome
buddies around,
you humans are pretty lame!
That's a good one, Drum!
♪
Intruders!
How did they
discover our location?
Shido led them right to us!
No!
♪
Ahh!
It wasn't me, I swear, you guys!
I couldn't have!
They found it on their own!
Grim Reaper,
where are you going?
This has nothing to do with me.
Get back here now!
This has everything
to do with you!
(yelling)
(laughing)
Look where you're going!
Hey, what's the big idea, Rouga?
I'm gonna show you.
One day, I'm gonna be
in charge like my father
and pay you back for all
the things you've done to me!
‐Hmm?
‐Huh?
If you two are
just about finished,
we have to make sure we prevent
them from getting any closer.
Oh, I wouldn't worry.
The guard robot should
take good care of them.
I don't know, are you sure
we're in the right place?
Hmm?
♪
Does that answer your question?
(grunting)
We've got company!
I'll take out those tin heads!
No, you can't!
Buddy monsters aren't allowed
to use their true
powers in our world.
It's dangerous.
Yeah, but you don't
have your Core Gadget.
I have something even better.
Huh‐‐whoa!
Okay, Captain Answer,
lend me your strength!
Time to release
the Future Force!
Future Force: On!
♪
‐Einder!
‐Zweider!
Dreider!
Together, we're the
Triple Rangers Quartet Five!
Awesome, I love these guys!
They're okay, I guess.
If you're into
that kind of thing.
♪
I don't understand, how do
they have such amazing power?
By the looks of it, they've
got Captain Answer's deck.
♪
Why can't I see them?
Are they behind me?
♪
‐It's Card Burn.
‐You think?
Let me officially introduce
you to our Disaster Force!
Guillotine Cutter!
♪
Okay, you guys, it's up to you.
Cool!
I cast‐‐I block
all your attacks.
He's neutralized the power
of the Disaster Force!
Of course he did.
Didn't you know those
robots were only created
when Tasuku brought
cards from the Hero World
here into reality?
I'm going to wipe them all out
with my Death Ruler, Curse!
Combine...
Ultimate Card Burn!
Stack up!
Hyper Card Fusion!
When Card Burn, Card Rhino,
and Card Serpent join forces,
the King of Cards appears from
the far reaches of Hero World!
♪
And his name is...
Strongest King,
Ultimate Card Burn!
♪
This is it, beware the blade
of justice that defeats evil!
Summoning Double Sword!
♪
‐That's far enough.
‐Huh?
Our master's asked me
to give you a message.
We do not desire to fight
or engage in battle with you.
We wish to talk.
What's Shido doing here?
That's Davide!
What‐‐Rouga?
Yeah, that girl
looks familiar, too!
The people here are special.
Our one destiny has united us.
Together we will
change the world.
I'm destined to lose my lunch.
We are Disaster.
We will free the
world from the adults
who control and manipulate it.
And give children
the voice they deserve.
I can't believe
what I'm hearing!
Where's the Grim Reaper?
I know he's one of
you‐‐point him out!
Call off your dog, Mikado.
Gao.
The Grim Reaper went this way.
You fool!
You two go after the Reaper.
Hmm‐‐but‐‐
I'll be okay.
I'm pretty sure I
can handle these guys.
Good luck‐‐we
shouldn't be too long.
‐You with me, Drum?
‐Duh!
♪
You must be the one in charge
of this Disaster or whatever.
Come down here and tell
me why you're giving out
all these Dark Core Deck cases!
You should show some respect.
Kyoya Gaen, just as I suspected.
As head of the
Gaen Financial Group,
you could've used your
influence in more positive ways.
So why this?
My deck!
But how did you‐‐?
Huh‐‐hey, what do
you think you're doing?
Can't you see, we were chosen.
You and I can make
the world better.
Adults are the ones responsible
for the real
disasters on our planet.
And they never learn
from their mistakes.
Now it's our turn.
What are you talking about?
All I ask is that you hear me
out, then make up your mind.
I could use someone with
your specialized expertise.
Huh?
But first, prove that
you're as good as they say
by winning a Buddyfight.
There'll be time for
your questions after that.
Hmm‐‐it's a deal.
Your opponents,
Davide and Shido.
Huh‐‐why two against one?
Yeah, Davide can go solo.
Because Tasuku's power is great,
and besides, you should never
question the master's orders.
Are we clear?
I have no objection.
I don't care how many there are!
♪
Freeze‐‐it's rude
to sneak up on people!
For that, I'm giving
you the cold shoulder!
I'm kinda getting used to this!
Easy for you to say,
you're warm‐blooded!
Hey, Grim Reaper,
you gonna fight us?
♪
Kiri!
Huh‐‐Kiri?
You don't have to hide it.
We know it's you!
Now let's do this.
♪
Why are you going around taking
buddies away from everyone?
Take off that ridiculous
mask and show us your face!
I'm not Kiri.
At least not anymore.
I'm the Reaper.
♪
This is definitely my deck,
but I don't recognize this card.
Any day now, Shido,
we're all waiting for you.
Stop telling me what to do!
To defeat and
humiliate all my enemies,
Dark Luminize, Black
Cloud of Endless Doom!
I'd rather take care of
the do‐gooder Buddy cop
all by myself.
Oh, well, what can you do?
It rocks so hard, it crushes!
Dark Luminize, The Black Dragon!
I wonder if this card is some
kind of challenge from Kyoya.
If that's the case, all
I can do is accept it.
Hey, hey, what's wrong?
Not scared, are ya?
I guess facing two of us
is more than he can handle.
He's scared speechless.
Huh, not quite.
You guys couldn't be more wrong.
‐Huh?
‐What?
To me, Jack's not
just an ordinary buddy,
he's family, and
now I'm lucky enough
to get to fight
alongside him once again.
Assemble Dragon Army‐‐
Dragonic Force, Luminize!
‐Raise the flag!
Darkness Dragon World!
Dragon World!
(roaring)
Hey, Jack, great to
see you, old friend.
You ready for this?
I don't know, that depends.
On what?
If you mean kicking
their butts, you bet!
All right.
Charge and draw!
To the right, I Buddy
Call Jackknife Dragon!
(grunting)
(roaring)
‐It's time for...
‐Tasuku and Gao's
Card of the Day!
Today we'll introduce you
to the card Death
Ruler, Gallows.
Its attack and defense are low,
but it has a cool ability
that lets it bypass
the center monster
and attack the fighter directly!
It's known as Shadow Dive!
What's cool is it can
also regain one life point
whenever it inflicts damage!
Yeah, man, it's
definitely a card you want
in your Darkness
Dragon World deck!
So what do you think, guys?
Think you can open
up one of these?
You'll never know until you try!
♪
Next time, the mysterious card
that Kyoya put in Tasuku's deck
is a special rare
with a forbidden power!
And will Gao and Kiri
finally break the ice?
Next episode,
Disaster Times Two!
It's Buddyfighting like
you've never seen it!