Get ready for a cool new
card game that connects
to a parallel universe.
Special cards act as portals
bringing monsters to Earth
to become buddies with humans,
and through friendship
and courage help them take
on fight challenges.
It's called Buddyfight.
Come on, Drum.
Stop being such a grump.
We're no longer buddies!
Whatever, stay
here and sulk then.
Huh!
(grunts)
(banging noise)
Hmmm.
There's something
sketchy about that cat.
♪
Hi, Gao!
Oh, hey, guys!
Hey, so where's Drum?
Don't know, don't care.
You two are fighting again?
So what's the deal this time?
Arguing over the last donut?
No, it was chocolate pudding and
I didn't even know it was his.
I just wanted a snack and
he freaked out as usual.
The guy's way too
emotional about food.
I'll show him emotional and
I'll teach him to steal my food!
♪
Today, I'm very pleased to
welcome your new classmate.
I'm Kiri Hyoryu.
It's nice to meet all of you.
I shouldn't have
called him lizard brain.
I guess he must be
pretty mad at me.
Thank you, Kiri, hmm?
You're the mighty sun fighter!
‐Huh?
‐Remember me?
You saved me from those bullies.
I've been telling
everyone what you did.
Right, so how's it going?
I can't believe I'm actually
going to be in the same class
as the mighty sun fighter!
Looks like you've
got a fan, Gao.
Okay, Kiri, we're about
to start the lesson now.
Right.
My name's Gao Mikado
but you can call me Gao.
The way you handled those
bullies, I was sure you were
in junior high school.
Yeah, I get that a lot.
Guess I'm mature for my age.
I'm just really happy
I got into this place.
I wasn't sure if I'd
be accepted or not.
I mean, Aibo Academy is one
of the super elite schools
in the country for
training buddy fighters.
Guess Gao's got a new pal.
Please turn your English
books to page 10.
I can't believe that puny human!
And as far as us being buddies,
I'm totally done with it!
(stomach growl)
(groan)
This is so weird.
It's not like him to miss lunch.
I'd never hear the end of
it if I ate both of these.
So what should I do?
Oh, man, oh.
Hey there, Gao!
Uh, uh, Kiri!
Do you mind if I sit here beside
you and join you for lunch?
Uh, no, not at all.
I sure hope Drum's
not still mad at me.
Ah, I'd better find him
and smooth things over.
Oh, hi there, Gao!
Uh, oh, hey.
Want to walk home together?
That's totally cool that
we're going to be in the same
Buddyfight class.
Yeah, I was kind of
hoping you could coach me
in Buddyfighting.
I don't know, I just
started Buddyfighting
so I'm not sure I'm
the right teacher.
Oh, I understand.
Hey, I got it!
I'll introduce you to
the best teacher I know.
Relax, you're not too
young to Buddyfight.
I've even seen five
year olds playing it.
Yeah, well, I didn't start
playing till sixth grade.
Okay, first up you
gotta choose a world.
Ginga!
Huh, coming.
Is that a robot?
He's a Superspace Robo Galaxy
Demon and he's my buddy.
It's important to remember that
cards are grouped according
to their type.
Now we call these
different groups worlds.
The Dragon World cards are
pretty cool 'cause they have
a good balance of
offense and defense.
While the Danger World cards
are known more for their
super powerful and
speedy attacks.
They're both relatively
easy to handle.
Hey, maybe you should
pick Dragon World like me.
‐I can be the same as you?
‐Hee!
Even though I want to be
like Gao, I won't improve
just copying him all the time.
Okay, I think I'll
go with Danger World.
All right, then, why
don't we get started?
‐What?
‐Hee.
I'm gonna give Gao
a piece of my mind!
(stomach growls)
Right after I eat.
Whoa something smells good.
Instead of me explaining
the rules to you,
I think you'll learn way faster
by playing the game yourself.
Your chariot awaits.
Let's go, ha!
I'll go get everything ready.
'Kay!
This is surreal man!
You know how lucky we are to be
using the castle fighting stage?
I can guess.
‐Huh?
‐Epic, right?
I'll be here if you need help.
Thanks.
Huh, get ready!
♪
Sorry for the wait but, hey,
check out my core gadget.
Super Demon Helmet.
That outfit is sweet!
Ha‐ha.
Are you ready, Kiri?
To start the proceedings we'll
each have 10 life points, okay?
And the first one to drop
all 10 loses the fight.
Okay, so if I inflict 10
damage points against you first,
‐then I win?
‐You got it, little dude.
Okay, now let's
luminize our decks.
Uh?
Trial deck luminize.
‐What's this?
‐An all‐purpose core gadget.
By putting your deck on top
of it, you can luminize it
even though you don't
have a core deck case.
Luminize!
‐Ah!
‐Ha!
Okay, so next you need to charge
two cards in the gauge zone,
all right?
The core gadget will
automatically set them for you.
They're those big, glowing
cards to your left.
I'll tell you all
about gauge later.
You've got enough on
your plate right now.
Listen up, now when I give you
the signal, you need to call out
raise the flag, Danger World!
‐You got it?
‐Um.
Ready?
Buddyfight!
‐Raise the flag!
Dragon World.
Danger World.
Since this is just
a practice game,
we won't be using
a Buddy monster.
In order to explain
everything to you properly,
I'll need to see your cards.
Why don't you go first?
Call a monster, any one you
want, just be sure to call it
to the center.
I call this one to the center.
Ogre!
‐Ah!
‐Good call.
He looks pretty strong.
Buddyfight is one
ultra fast game, dude.
Remember, the guy who goes
first could attack only once.
Now it's time to give that
mighty monster of yours
a command!
Armorknight Ogre, go
and attack the manager!
Ogre!
Come on, bring it!
O‐burn!
End of move.
‐Yes!
‐Ah?
You see, Ogre's critical
is two, leaving the manager
with eight points.
Wow, Buddyfighting is super fun.
Get your dumplings,
red hot dumplings here.
You must be from Dragon World.
Do you have any Earth
money, by chance?
Is your buddy nearby?
I don't really have
a buddy right now.
I used to but we're
kind of on the outs.
Here, eat this.
Are you sure?
It's my treat.
Hmm, they're delicious!
Glad you like them.
My family's recipe has been
handed down for generations.
Maybe I can give you some
friendly advice about the whole
situation with you
and your buddy.
Try looking him in the eye and
listening to what he has to say.
Take it from me,
these disagreements
tend to resolve themselves.
Have these, you can share
them with your buddy, 'kay?
Wow, thanks.
Yeah!
‐Yeah!
‐Woo, cool!
The player who starts the
game can only attack once.
The one going second draws
a card and begins the game
with a hand of seven cards.
So who has the advantage, the
fighter going first or second?
You'd think going first
would be best, huh, dude?
But according to the stats,
the winning percentages
are just about even.
Get ready, 'cause I'm
gonna call my monster.
I call Bronze Shield
Dragon to the center.
Argh!
And I also call Extreme Sword
Dragon to the left position.
♪
Yah!
Two of them?
All the monsters come
in different sizes.
Whatever you call can't
add up to more than three,
like three size one monsters
or one size three monster.
Exactly.
Now I'm gonna attack you
with my two monsters, 'kay?
But oh, no, I can't 'cause
you got Ogre at your center!
Ogre!
As long as a player has
a monster at the center,
they can't be directly attacked.
So it's, like, protecting me!
I have no choice.
Extreme Sword Dragon,
attack Ogre!
In a fight between
monsters like this,
their power and
defense become key.
‐Uh?
‐Take a look.
Extreme Sword Dragon's power
is 5,000 and Ogre's defense
is just 3,000, so when power
is greater than defense...
♪
Ogre!
And just like that your
center monster is toast.
Bronze Shield Dragon,
attack Kiri!
‐Uh!
‐Ah!
End of move.
Now over to you, Kiri.
Your move.
Draw a card.
Just touch the core gadget
and it'll draw for you.
Huh?
Each time you draw a card,
they're automatically shuffled
so your opponent isn't able
to see what you're up to.
Wow.
You remember charging those
two cards in the gauge zone
at the beginning, right?
Yes.
Well, you're allowed to put
one card from your hand
onto the gauge
and draw another card.
Hang on a sec.
If I charge one
card from my hand,
am I allowed to
draw another card?
Uh‐huh, but only
once during each turn.
We call this charge and draw.
So can you tell me now
what the gauge is for?
When you play stronger
cards, you pay a cost.
The gauge is what you use to
make these so‐called payments.
Then it's like depositing
the cards in a bank?
You're catching on.
Try and add to your
gauge every turn.
What's this?
Boulder piercing spear?
You got the boulder
piercing spear?
That there is
called an item card.
You equip yourself with that
and then you can take part
in the battle.
Go on, equip yourself.
'Kay, equip boulder
piercing spear.
‐Cool!
‐You're frying my brain.
With that card, you've
just gained the ability
to attack with 2 critical
points and 3,000 power.
But remember, you can't use it
as long as there's a monster
in your center because
then you'd end up attacking
your own guy in the back.
Okay, I guess I'll
call Armorknight Ogre
to the right!
And I'll call Armorknight
Minotaur to the left!
The triple offensive maneuver,
oh, man, that's
my favorite formation.
Gee, thanks, Gao, your
support means a lot.
Sorry to dampen your excitement,
guys, but at my center I have
Bronze Shield Dragon
with 6,000 defense.
My boulder piercing spear
has only 3,000 power
and Ogre and Minotaur
have just 5,000 power each.
It won't be enough.
‐Kiri?
‐Huh?
You should use a link attack.
Link attack, what's that?
By attacking with
the two things at once,
your power becomes
the total of the two.
So if I combine Ogre's
power with mine...
That'll be a total
of 8,000, not good!
Ogre, let's attack Bronze
Shield Dragon together!
‐Ogre!
‐Aaaah!
♪
Ha!
Aah!
Ogre!
My Bronze Shield Dragon!
And now, Minotaur,
attack the manager!
Ha!
Here, catch, aah!
Ugh!
End of move.
A link attack, nicely done.
Way to go, Kiri!
That's Gao!
Draw, charge and draw!
Systemic Dagger
Dragon to the center!
Rarh!
Systemic Dagger, attack Ogre!
‐Oh, yeah!
‐Ogre!
‐Extreme Sword attack!
Ah!
End of move.
You learn fast.
Welcome to the world
of Buddyfighting, dude.
Uh, thanks.
Draw, charge and draw.
I call Bloodwind Dragon,
Elyrseagard to the right.
My boulder piercing spear has
3,000 power and my opponent's
Systemic Dagger Dragon
has 3,000 defense.
What happens when
they're the same?
Attacking side wins.
This is for Ogre!
Rarh!
Elyrseagard, attack the manager!
‐Cast!
‐What's that?
I'll pay one gauge
for dragon breath.
Ah!
Minotaur, attack the manager!
Cast the Green Dragon Shield.
(roar)
End of move.
Your move.
The Green Dragon Shield
guarded against the attack
and I get a life point back.
Draw, charge and draw.
I call Thousand Rapier
Dragon to the center
and also cast dragonic destroy!
I'm gonna pay two gauge
to eliminate one monster!
Thousand Rapier and
Extreme Sword, attack Kiri!
Yah!
End of move.
Uh, sorry, sometimes I
get a little carried away.
Your move.
Mm, and draw.
Oh, no!
Come on, you still
have a chance.
Charge and draw.
‐Yes!
‐What?
Did you just draw the most
powerful monster in the deck??
Go, Kiri, give him
everything you got!
Okay.
I'll pay three gauge and
call Armorknight Black Drake
to the left.
♪
(roar)
But I have Thousand Rapier
Dragon at my center.
You'll have to remove him with
your boulder piercing spear
and what'll you do after that?
Your monster only
has four critical.
With my six life points,
it's not gonna be enough.
‐What if I use this?
‐What?
I thought you hadn't
even noticed that card.
This is bad.
I cast crimson slash!
Ah!
Huh, Black Drake,
attack the manager!
Rah, have some of this!
Oh!
And a bit of this!
Keep going, Kiri!
Ha, yah!
Ah!
Uh, you got me.
Game over, winner, Kiri Hyoryu.
Whoo!
(applause)
Wow, Buddyfight is amazing!
You know it!
All the huge monsters
and powerful magic,
I can't believe
I never tried it before.
This is the greatest
feeling ever!
But you're still missing
one thing... a buddy.
Having a great buddy
like Drum makes the game
even more exciting.
Wait a sec, did he
say "great buddy"?
Buddyfighting as a team is epic
no matter if you win or lose.
‐Yeah?
‐Nope, only if you win.
So you're a beginner.
Well, the Danger World
is an excellent choice.
Excellent choice.
Yeah, I thought so, too.
‐Hey, kid?
‐Yes?
Now that you've
picked the Danger World,
you'd better be prepared
to show some determination.
Determination?
No matter who you fight,
do what you must to win.
That's what'll make you
stronger, trust me.
Uh, you mean if I try hard,
even I can get good?
Of course.
Just remember this, the only
thing of any value in this world
‐is winning.
‐Gotta win it.
‐I don't think so.
‐Huh?
Sure, winning's
pretty important.
I mean, you won't hear
me arguing about that,
but I don't think
it's the only thing.
Who are you?
My name's Gao, Gao
Mikado, to be exact.
I'm kind of new to Buddyfighting
but I know that doing your best,
win or lose, is what any game
is all about, am I right?
Trust me, in the world of
Buddyfighting sometimes doing
your best isn't enough.
Wait till you have a few losses.
Later, kids.
Hey, it's those
two from the alley.
Huh?
I'm gonna pay you back
for the other day,
you whatchamacallit fighter.
What are you doing here?
Hey, it's not me.
This'll be fun.
Really?
You're banned from the store
'cause you threatened kids
and tried stealing their cards.
Yeah, right, why don't you
fight us for the cards then?
It's okay, I can take
these guys on my own.
But, Gao, your buddy's
not even here, dude!
Huh?
Forever alone, ha ha ha!
‐Hey!
‐Huh?
You're not bothering
my buddy here, are ya?
Hey, heya, pal!
You think we're gonna
run away just 'cause
your buddy showed up?
I don't think so.
‐Raise the flag!
Dragon World.
Prepare to lose, punks.
Danger World!
Crash, drill ramp bunker!
Steel fist dragoknuckle!
Ah!
Game over, winner, Gao Mikado.
Yeah, now that's how it's done.
I'll get you for this.
That was amazing.
Hey, uh, well, I'm really
sorry about what happened.
What do you mean?
Gah, so you're not going to
make this easy for me, huh?
Even though I didn't
know it was yours,
it was still my fault for
eating your pudding, sorry.
Here, you want some?
Uh, maybe... what is it?
They're probably
cold by now, though.
I love octopus dumplings
even when they're cold.
Huh?
Hey, there's only one
dumpling left in the box!
Now you know how I
felt about the pudding!
No way, maybe if I'd
eaten four helpings!
You gonna eat it, 'cause
if not, I'll have it.
Someday, I hope to be lucky
enough to get a buddy like Drum.
A mine in Mount Fuji?
That's where you'll
find the photon mill.
I'd like you to retrieve
some and bring it here.
Whatever the cost?
Do what is necessary, Aragami.
So is that an
official order then?
Always questioning my authority.
Why, do I look like I'm joking?
Hmm, I couldn't care less
who's in charge of this,
so long as I'm the one
who gets to test the power
of this dark core.
♪
You're dismissed.
Dark core activate
disaster force.
♪
(screams)
(evil laughter)
Armorknight Cerberus.
♪
We're here, Rouga.
Don't call me that.
My name at this moment is Wolf.
Cerberus.
Dark buddy skill on.
♪
Let's give them something
they'll never forget.
(evil laughter)
Hello there, I'm Paruko,
here to guide you through
the world of Buddyfight.
You already know that
a core deck case is given
to a Buddyfighter from the
Buddycard office, right?
Well, did you know that
even if your opponent
doesn't have a core deck case,
the deck can be
temporarily luminized
with the use of an
all‐purpose core gadget,
because when a
deck is luminized,
monsters and spells and
all kinds of crazy things
appear to make the fight all
the more super exciting, right?
Can you open a Buddy rare card?
What do you think?
The mysterious Buddyfighter
Wolf somehow makes the power
of the cards real, like
real weapons and magic.
This isn't Buddyfight!
Next episode:
Join us for a Buddyfight!