Get ready for a
cool new card game
that connects to a
parallel universe.
Special cards act as portals,
bringing monsters to Earth
to become buddies with humans,
and through friendship
and courage,
help them take
on fight challenges.
It's called Buddyfight!
Huh?
One who calls forth Calamity.
This world shall be tainted red.
Demon Way Karakurenai.
♪
Game over.
Winner, Jin Magatsu.
Awesome, talk about
a finishing move!
FYI, everyone, the first
round match of the ABC Cup
between president of the
student council, Shido,
and Noboru Kodo of Team Rising
Tiger will be held after lunch.
‐Don't be late!
‐Hey, that's my food!
‐You wanna go, I called dibs!
‐That's mine!
‐Mine, mine, mine!
‐I already gave you some!
Hey, what's that?
You let your guard
down, you lose.
Mmmm.
Hey, so your team finally
hits the stage next, huh?
Huh, you talking
about Noboru's fight?
We're not really doing anything,
he just used our names
to make up the numbers.
Oh, you're not gonna be helping
him out in the buddy pit?
‐Uh...
Huh.
♪
That's Dragon Knight,
Vlad Dracula, isn't it?
♪
You've been carrying
it around for a while.
Why haven't you put it
into your deck already?
It's a very powerful card.
Yeah, but Vlad's
difficult to control.
Adding it to my
deck would totally
throw the balance way off.
‐It's just not worth the hassle.
‐Take a listen to yourself.
Don't you have the confidence to
build the deck you truly want?
‐Maybe not.
‐What's this?
It sounds to me like
you're a little scared.
I'm not scared.
We all have our fears.
Wait up, I'll join
you for lunch.
♪
‐He wants to see you.
‐Huh?
Hey, you're from
the student council.
Come with me, it's important.
♪
You did well for me
at last year's ABC Cup.
Thanks to you I didn't
have to waste time trying.
I'm hoping for more of the same.
Can I count on you again?
Uh...
Now, which card would you
like to take this year?
♪
Whoa, look at all
the Dragon Knights!
You even have Vlad Dracula!
Take it if you want it.
You really mean it?
All right!
Wow, thanks, I've
always wanted this one!
So, what is it you wanted
to talk to me about?
I gave you exactly
what you wanted
when I handed you that card.
Now it's only fair that in
return you do the same for me.
‐Quid pro quo.
‐Oh.
If it should happen
that we face each other
in the ABC Cup, well‐‐
You want me to lose
to you on purpose?
Shh, keep your voice down, okay?
But there's no way I could
do that, it's just wrong!
You know what would be wrong
is accepting a generous gift
from someone and giving
nothing in return.
Then I don't want it,
here, have it back!
‐Huh?
‐You don't get it.
Vlad Dracula is yours.
You took is as part of
a binding agreement to lose
your fight against me
in the tournament.
Now do we understand
one another?
♪
Game over, winner,
Magoroku Shido.
What a match, with that defeat,
Noboru's surprising
run has come to an end,
but don't worry, you younger
fans, there's still one
fifth grader left in the
tournament to cheer for.
‐I don't want your card.
‐Huh?
Don't worry, I'll still
do what you want.
I'll lose the fight
and let you beat me.
Good, it helps
us both, you know.
At least this way you don't have
to worry about losing to Gao.
I just hope we get
to meet in the finals.
Hm.
You still haven't even
fought against Zanya Kisaragi,
the top ranked fighter
in your grade,
and yet you've kept
your number two ranking.
I like your style, kid, by not
challenging that top position
you're able to avoid
the agony of defeat.
To me that's the mark
of a true winner.
Shido, he's gone already.
I know I'm a much better
player than that kid.
He's no real threat, but one
can never be too careful.
♪
(indistinct conversations)
Hey, Noboru.
About your match against
Shido this afternoon‐‐
We both wanna do whatever we can
to help you out
in the buddy pit.
I just used your
names to qualify.
I don't want any of your help!
♪
So, what're you going
to do about that card?
There's nothing
to do, like I said,
I don't wanna mess with
the balance of my deck.
Use the card, my boy, and fight
with the best deck you can.
Take some advice from an old man
who's had his fair
share of regrets.
Sure, it's true you're old
enough to do as you wish,
but a knight will
always meet his destiny,
even on the road
he takes to avoid it.
You're an excellent
buddyfighter.
The balance you seek
will come from within you.
And we're back at the ABC Cup.
In this final match of the first
round we've got Magoroku Shido,
our hardworking president
of the student council,
up against Noboru Kodo
of Team Rising Tiger.
Remember, these two also
met first round last year
with our prez coasting
to an easy victory.
So will we see the
same result this time?
Or has another year
of training given Noboru
the skills to dominate?
It's the moment
of truth, people!
Man, I was super choked he
didn't fight better last year.
‐Did you mean Noboru?
‐Yeah.
It was weird, because
he's always been known
for turning out decks
that are wickedly balanced.
Well, then maybe he'll be able
to beat him this time around.
I don't know, balanced
decks are definitely sweet,
but they don't always cut it.
It's tough to win with
just a balanced deck.
See, you need a powerful
card to win the big fights.
Remember, bro, you gotta
focus on one major card
or skill and build
your deck around it.
It makes me think though, Noboru
must have some incredible skills
to be able to retain
his number two ranking
‐with a balanced deck alone.
‐Yeah.
The guy has no clue
how primetime savage
he could be out there.
‐Hey, where's Gao?
‐Huh?
(background chatter)
‐Hey, glad you made it.
‐Sup?
I wonder if it's really true.
"I thought you should know
that Genma's Koryukien deck
is hidden in the student
council's office."
What?
There's only one way
to know for sure.
I knew it!
Huh?
Big brother, I don't get
why you're going through
all this trouble.
You'll see soon enough.
♪
With Noboru on my side, this
should be over in no time.
I will turn you into ashes.
Luminize!
Dangerous Killer Death!
It sounds like our big boss
Shido means business.
Luminize, knights unleashed!
Come on, everyone,
say it like you mean it!
Buddy...
fight!
‐Time to raise the flag.
I fight for Danger World.
I'm with Dragon World.
♪
‐Noboru will go first.
‐Let's go.
See if you've learned
anything since last year.
♪
That's it, my boy,
follow your heart.
Above all else, a true knight
is honorable in battle.
Thanks for believing in me.
I won't let you down.
Hm, at last,
the boy finally has the
courage to be himself.
♪
Charge and Draw!
I Buddy Call Dragon Knight,
El Quixote to center!
Beelining it to
the Buddy Call, huh?
Guess that only means one thing.
Thou hast seen nothing yet!
El Quixote, attack the fighter!
Here we go, Rocinante!
An assault of glory.
(shouting)
End of move.
Only two life points?
You could at least try making
it a little more convincing.
I don't know what you mean.
I plan on winning
this match, Shido.
If an El Quixote attack
causes damage to a fighter
then I get one gauge added.
From where I'm standing, I'd
say it was an excellent move.
It seems you've had a
slight change of heart
as to our arrangement.
No worries, I'll just
beat you on my own.
Your move.
Draw, Charge and Draw.
First I'll show
that clumsy old suit
of armor some of my virtues.
Cast.
‐Crimson Slash!
‐Never surrender!
♪
Now I call Armorknight
Minotaur to the center,
and Armorknight Ogre
to the right.
And I Buddy Call Bluechase
Dragon, Garg to the left.
‐Ogre!
‐Ahh!
Amazing, President
Shido has pulled out
three monsters at once!
Nothing like stating the
obvious, but Noboru seems
‐to be in a heap of trouble.
‐Prepare yourselves
for the magnificent
spectacle of Danger World.
This quarter‐final match will
be over in just a few moments.
I'm going to thrash
this kid and prove
that beating him last
year was no fluke.
Now, attack that poor
excuse for a buddyfighter.
Ogre!
♪
‐End of move.
‐Come on, man!
I'll teach him to back
out of a deal with me.
My monsters will tear him apart.
This middle schooler's
not pulling any punches.
Noboru better do something
soon, or this might end up
being a rerun of
last year's fight.
I call Dragon Knight,
Red Baron to the left.
And Dragon Knight,
Masamune to the right.
♪
Now, by placing the Dragon
Knights that I just called
in the gauge, I can
call Dragon Knight,
Kamitsumiyaou to the center.
♪
‐Noboru seems different.
‐Mhm.
He looks the same to me.
♪
It's Dragon Knight,
Kamitsumiyaou.
As Noboru just explained, it
can only be called if a fighter
sends two Dragon Knights already
in the field to the gauge.
(roaring)
Okay, Kamitsumiyaou,
take out the Minotaur!
You're not planning on
backing out now, are you?
You're still sticking
with your fight strategy?
‐Yeah.
‐Good.
Then I will give you the power
you need to make it happen.
Seven Star Sword
Celestial Vortex!
♪
End of move.
This isn't the way
Noboru usually fights.
Yeah!
If you're going to bring
out a size three monster,
then so will I.
Draw.
Charge and Draw.
I'll pay two gauge,
and send Garg and Ogre
over to the drop zone.
Now I call.
Are you ready to be amazed?
To the center!
The king of all
monsters has arrived.
It dominates, devours,
and reigns supreme.
Behold Emperor
Dragon, Gael Khan.
Nice entrance, the king's roar.
(roaring)
Just by calling Gael Khan,
all opponent monsters
in the field are
immediately destroyed!
Stick to your plan for victory!
(laughing)
Get down on your knees
and grovel, Kitten Shirt.
You can't match
that kind of power.
With Kamitsumiyaou's
effect, I draw two cards.
When destroyed, Kamitsumiyaou's
special skill lets a player
draw two cards, but
hold the phone, guys.
Believe it or not, it's still
President Shido's turn!
There's no way I'm through yet.
I've still got some
monsters up my sleeve.
I call Garg to the left.
♪
Lastly, I now cast
set spell Night in the Wild.
‐What's a set spell?
‐It's a powerful spell card.
It actually remains in play
once it's set on the field.
Bro, by paying a gauge,
the Night in the Wild card
gives the player one life point.
And he gets to do it every turn?
Uh‐huh, so the longer
the match goes,
the more life points
he can rack up.
Just when we thought things
couldn't get any more one‐sided
out there, President Shido
increases his life points.
Let's see how this plays out.
And that's not
even my best card.
‐Garg, go and attack Noboru.
‐Not so fast!
Cast Dragon Breath!
(explosive noises)
Your lame moves are pointless.
Gael Khan, attack the fighter!
Show them all what a
superior fighter I am!
(growling)
End of move.
Is he okay?
Noboru's down to one life point.
It's all over but the crying.
‐Your move.
‐That's it!
I'm gonna end this now!
(laughing)
And how are you
going to do that?
Your one point to my ten?
I doubt that even I could
manage to beat me now.
Man, how does Noboru think
he'll get out of this one?
‐There's only one way.
‐Do you think he added it?
Added what, guys?
I call El Quixote to the right.
Carpe diem!
♪
I call Dragon Knight, Vlad
Dracula to the left position!
♪
At last, so my time has come.
I will not let you go
into the unknown alone,
young dragon warrior.
(laughing)
So you're finally
using the card.
We both know what you did
last year to get it, don't we?
Going back on your decision
now doesn't change
the kind of person
you really are.
Stop your blabbering.
How dare you call into
question Noboru's character?
Sure, he's made some wrong
choices on his journey,
but show me the
knight who hasn't!
At least he doesn't
manipulate people
for his own personal gain.
No matter how it was
acquired, Dragon Knight,
Vlad Dracula is Noboru's card.
You have no place commenting
on his right to use it.
Do I make myself clear?
Thank you, El Quixote.
Thank me when we've won.
I equip Twin Dragonblades,
Dragoanthem.
Say what, an item card?
Has he given up trying
to defend entirely?
♪
You've forgotten that Gael Khan
here has 10,000 defense.
Plus, I still have
10 life points.
So matter what half‐baked
plan you've got,
I'm still gonna come out
of this as the winner.
I cast Dragonic Destroy!
Destroy Gael Khan!
♪
Didn't quite see
that one coming.
Gael Khan's been wiped
out, way to go, Noboru!
By paying two gauge,
the Dragonic Destroy card
will demolish one
opponent's monster.
I can't believe you put
that card in your deck.
Everyone knows its cost
is too high for its effect.
Well, that explains it,
I'm not everyone.
I'm actually starting
to like this kid.
He's good, I hope we get to
fight him in the next round.
Me too.
(shouting)
♪
One more time, ha!
Hey, El Quixote,
attack the fighter!
With sword, steel, and courage!
♪
Now a final blow with Vlad.
But that would be impossible!
‐I have six life points.
‐Check out the stats.
My Vlad Dracula will
tell you what's possible.
‐Bloody Charge.
‐Bloody Charge?
If you didn't know, Vlad
Dracula's critical increases
with each Dragon Knight
that's in the drop zone.
♪
How did I forget that?
Young warrior, you did well
laying this path of victory.
You are a skilled fighter,
but never allow others
to make choices for you.
The biggest battle
is in the mind.
Master that and I will fight
with everything that I have!
Okay, I will!
Now, attack the fighter!
(indistinct) for life!
(screaming)
♪
‐Yeah!
‐Game over.
Winner, Noboru Kodo.
(cheering)
He reduced my life points
by ten in just one turn.
I guess everyone gets
lucky sometimes.
That wasn't luck,
it was strategy.
It came to me while
I was trying to fit
the Vlad Dracula
card into my deck.
That's gotta be the biggest
comeback I've ever seen!
Now that the president of the
student council's been defeated,
the only middle school
team left in the tournament
is Team Naniwa Card Club.
With three teams left
from the elementary school,
this string of upsets is
a first in ABC Cup history!
♪
(beeping)
Hey, Noboru!
‐Hm?
‐Nice match.
Save some for me, huh?
Oh, I will.
You can bet on it.
But you know what I'm
really looking forward to?
There is something
different about him.
Defeating both you
and Zanya on this stage
so I can win the ABC Cup.
Keep on dreaming, man.
‐Ah.
‐Something I can help you with?
‐When did you get here?
‐I'll never tell.
Listen to me, I
have to see Genma!
Perfect, I'll let him
know you're dropping in.
(screaming)
♪
(groaning)
I'll get them if it's
the last thing I do.
‐Doai.
‐Master Genma.
Are you all right?
Sir, have they really
taken the deck?
Yeah.
Hello there, I'm Paruko Nanana,
your guide to the
Buddyfight world.
Big, strong, and way cool.
Size three monsters
are the bomb,
but you need others too.
Like Noboru discovered,
the trick is to decide
what you wanna do ahead of time.
Then you can use other cards
to help advance your game plan.
Baku says that's the key
to building great decks,
and if anyone would
know, he would.
Can you open a Buddy Rare card,
what do you think?
♪
Tune in next time as
the first semifinal match
gets under way between
Gao and Noboru.
But is it true that
Noboru's planning
on studying at another school?
Join us for a Buddyfight:
Dragon's Duel,
Journey of the Tiger!