Do you have what it
takes to Buddyfight?
Choose your favorite world
and use special cards to
summon its powerful monsters
into reality.
Challenge other fighters
and Buddy Call
your toughest ally
to fight by your side.
Get ready to raise the flag!
(birds chirping)
Wish you were here, Yota.
I'll make you proud,
big brother.
♪
Teach that loser
a lesson, Gao.
(grimaces)
I mean, good luck out there!
Thanks, I think
we got a good shot.
Now, son, are you
sure about this?
Yeah, don't worry, Dad.
I just got to look at it
like a regular Buddyfight.
Well, the big
day is upon us.
The much
anticipated Buddyfight
between Kyoya Gaen
and Gao Mikado
is just hours away.
And as our very own voice
on the street poll revealed,
there are virtually
no supporters
for the Sun Fighter, Mikado,
who accuse him of rebellious
behavior towards our hero.
So much for a welcome party.
Don't let it bug you, Drum.
They're gonna see
the light eventually.
‐Hmm?
‐Huh?
♪
You all came.
Huh?
(helicopter blades whirring)
♪
Judging by
their flight path,
it looks like they're headed
straight for Mount Fuji.
The fighting stage
must be there.
Aren't you going to
notify the Buddy Police?
I don't think
we need to bother.
I'm sure they're
on top of things.
Target's on course
to expected destination.
Projected arrival time,
three minutes.
Besides, their
hands are tied
until Kyoya makes
the first move.
If they act too soon,
they'll be doing
exactly what he wants
and ruin any chance
they have of stopping him.
But if they wait
until he does something,
it'll be too late.
It's up to us to stop
him before that happens.
Then let's go.
♪
Don't worry, Gao,
we'll have your back.
I guess I'm not really
gonna be alone
out there, am I?
You humans are
slow on the uptake.
I was kinda surprised by
your text this morning, bro.
I'm getting used to
your last minute rush jobs,
but asking me
to tweak your deck
the morning of an
epic fight like this
is just harsh.
You weren't complaining
while you were
putting it together.
Why would I?
A deck builder's nothing
without his craft.
Even though we can't
be up there with you,
we'll be cheering you on.
That's right,
Team Balle du Soleil
be representin' everywhere.
So go out there and destroy
that annoying so‐called hero.
Y'all know you got this one.
Here's your new
Explosive Dragon Fang deck.
I balanced it so I could
add the card we talked about.
It looks awesome.
Thanks.
Since ancient times,
victory has gone
to the courageous.
It's time for you to
wield the power of the sun.
And don't you worry,
I'll take care of the
victory celebration.
I'll get my chef, Pierre,
to take care of the food
and yours truly will
oversee the decorations.
(helicopter blades churning)
It's not too late to
back out if you want.
I mean, it's a huge risk
what you're doing.
Walking away's
the smarter choice,
but you've always fought
the odds, haven't you?
No way, Gao wouldn't
bail on a fight.
'Cause to him, every opponent's
like a new best friend.
Right?
♪
Just promise me
something, Mikado,
wipe the floor
with that guy
and come back right away.
It's been a while since
our last Buddyfight.
(helicopter blades whirring)
♪
You ready, kid?
Yeah, let's do this!
♪
I think it's time
for our grand finale.
But Gremlin's not here and
I don't know where he is.
Don't worry about him.
His role in this
is done with anyway.
♪
And what about
Tasuku Ryuneji?
I'll leave him to you.
Da.
(electricity sparking)
This is going
to be beautiful.
The final piece of the plan
that will hide the sun
in total darkness.
Hi, everyone,
it's me, Paruko Nanana.
Wherever there's
a Buddyfight,
I'll be
reporting the action.
And I guess
you're all wondering
exactly where I am.
Well, I'm inside an
incredible state‐of‐the‐art
fighting stage that was
built under Mount Fuji
just for this match.
That's the leader of the
Gaen Financial Group for you.
He does everything
to the extreme.
Speaking of extreme,
I'm the only one
who's actually allowed
in the stadium!
So don't move a muscle,
and prepare yourselves for
the most exciting battle yet.
This perfect
contest will be
the first and
last of its kind!
♪
As you all know, Gaen Cup
Champion Gao Mikado
has been bold
enough to challenge
the amazing Mr. Kyoya Gaen.
I wonder what
kind of thoughts
are racing
through his mind
as he stands up there
with the weight of
today's fight upon him?
Welcome to my private
stage, Mr. Mikado.
Thanks for coming.
To unite the ones who dare,
I will become
the final destroyer!
Dark Luminize,
Wings of Demise!
The most powerful deck ever,
blazing a path
to the future!
Luminize!
Explosive Dragon Fang!
Buddy...
Fight!
‐Time to raise the flag.
I fight with Dragon World!
What's this?
Did Kyoya actually just
forget to raise his flag?
My flag requires
something extra.
Give me a moment.
Activate Disaster Force.
There, now I'm ready
to change the world.
Well, we all know
he's big on surprises,
but I'm sure no one
expected Kyoya himself
to be a user of
the Disaster Force.
But there's much more.
Wait until
you see my flag.
Dragon Ein.
Hold the phone!
Can anyone tell
me what that is?
Oh, right,
no one else is here.
It's just like Tasuku
said it would be.
Dragon Ein?
His flag's unique.
It doesn't represent
a specific world
like yours or mine.
It's special.
It allows him
to use any card
that has dragon
in its attributes.
It limits him to
four cards in his hand,
but he starts out with
twelve life points.
We're up against a flag card
that has its own ability.
I can't believe that
kind of thing even exists!
I've been
announcing for ages.
Why haven't I
heard about this?
I'd like a rule
confirmation, please.
Is something like
that even allowed?
Of course it is.
And that's
because I'm the one
who actually approved it.
Hey, Tasuku, what brings
you all the way out here?
Come to beg Kyoya
to take you back?
Not gonna happen.
Disaster Force, activate!
Move aside, Shido.
Look, he's got
Kiri with him, too.
Remember how weak he was
before we helped him?
This is gonna be fun.
We don't want
to fight you guys.
I don't think
we have a choice.
(evil laughter)
I'll tear you
limb from limb!
Time to release
the Future Force!
♪
That's okay, I needed
a warm‐up anyway.
Be there soon, Gao.
Dragobreak!
♪
Come on, give me
your best shot.
(yells)
Freeze!
This is my Rune Staff.
I'm going to use it to
stop you in your tracks.
Is that supposed
to scare me?
Bring it!
Hurry up, get over
there and attack.
You should watch it.
My gluteus maximus!
♪
Let's go to work.
Just stick to
the game plan.
You got it.
Eclipsing the
darkness with flames.
And brightening the
hearts of the mistreated.
The Mighty Sun
Fighter is here!
Now, let's get
started already.
Here it comes,
the challenger, Gao,
has the first
move of the match.
Charge and draw.
I call Thousand Rapier Dragon
to the center position.
Go on, attack the fighter!
Hmm.
Inferal Veritas!
End of move.
As he's never been seen
in competition before,
all eyes are sure to be
fixed on Kyoya's first move.
I draw and
charge and draw.
I cast Dragon
Emperor Legend.
That spell increases
his life gauge
and the cards
in his hand all by one.
Interesting, that card
is from Ancient World.
So he can use spell cards
with dragon in
the attribute, too?
Next I chose to cast
Divine Dragon Creation.
He just gave up
two life points
to increase the number
of cards in his hand.
For my next move,
I'll set the spell,
Dragon Throne.
I'm at a loss.
I don't know that card.
It's a spell that
can only be played
when the Dragon
Ein flag is used.
It boosts the maximum size
of monsters I can call
from three to four.
He's kidding, right?
Did he say size four?
None of my spells
or items in the field
can be destroyed
or returned to my hand.
What it means is that
the Dragon Throne spell
can never be undone.
Say what?
How can anyone have
such a crazy ability, huh?
Let me show you
how it works.
Call.
Thunder Knights,
Drum Bunker Dragon
to the right position.
And Thunder Knights,
Halberd Dragon to the left.
He can call two size two
monsters at the same time?
Of all the monsters,
why those ones?
♪
(electricity zapping)
Are we on schedule?
Come and see for yourself.
With enough energy,
this machine will create
a mini black hole,
causing a dimensional shift.
It's just a matter of time
before the Dark Core
Deck Case replicas
can gather enough
Disaster Force
from all of the unsuspecting
children using them.
Once that power's harnessed,
we can finally open
the giant portal
to Darkness Dragon World.
But the boy is still
the key to it all.
Meaning Gao Mikado,
the one with the greatest
Disaster Force potential.
If he awakens
that tremendous power
lying dormant within him,
the portal will
open at once.
I'm well aware of that.
Why else do you thing Master
Kyoya brought him here?
He wants him
to be the person
who brings about
the end of the world.
Thunder Knights Drum,
set your drill
on Thousand Rapier.
Go attack!
♪
Penetrate.
(screaming)
I almost forgot‐‐the
amazing Disaster Force
makes the power of
the cards into reality.
Time to show
your strength, Halberd.
Attack the fighter!
(Gao screams)
End of move.
Ugh, uh, he's strong.
With moves like that,
I can see why he beat
Tasuku in a match.
What do you want,
his autograph?
You okay, Gao,
can you still go on?
I'm just getting started.
Uhh, draw!
Uh, charge and draw!
Time to look alive,
'cause I Buddy Call!
Drum, go over to the right!
Oh, yeah!
Systemic Dagger Dragon,
to the left!
And I call Boomerang
Dragon to the center!
Let's go get
that dunny rat.
Yes, very good,
don't hold back.
Show me all of your
power and strength!
I equip my mighty
Dragon Blade Drumsword.
There it is, the next
generation Gao formation!
I move Thunder Knight's
Drum to the center.
Go clear me a path
through the center, Drum.
With pleasure, kid.
(grunting)
Today's not your
day, look‐alike,
when it comes
to a drill fight,
I'm the best there is.
I've trained
in other worlds.
Nice job.
Boomerang Dragon!
I'm going off
like a frog in a sock.
Argh, go get him!
You're a real beauty!
Uh, come on,
Dagger, our turn.
Excellent!
Danse Macabre!
♪
(yelling)
I cast Black Dragon Shield.
You're not strong
enough to defeat me.
End of move.
You'll see, Mikado.
Soon your need for
victory will consume you
and you'll have no choice
but to use the
Disaster Force.
Your move.
I draw.
Charge and draw.
I call Crash Dragon,
Gael Korga to the right.
And Death Dragon,
Deathgaze Dragon
to the center.
This is a first!
Three dragons from
different worlds
fighting together?
Clearly there's no holds
barred in this fight!
This Dragon Ein is amazing.
A flag that can
transcend worlds.
Gael Korga attack
the fighter!
I cast White Dragon Shield!
That's it, Gao,
defense is the key.
Deathgaze,
go attack Dagger!
I cast Green
Dragon Shield!
That's one of those
scary darkness
Dragon World monsters, yo.
Okay, Halberd,
attack the fighter!
I'm all out of shields!
(screams)
End of move.
Somehow Gao managed
to survive that round,
but he's clearly outmatched.
It's just a matter
of time before he falls
to Kyoya's
exceptional skill.
Check out that Dragon Ein.
It's totally wicked.
Wish I could get my
hands on one of those.
(yells)
You all right?
Yeah, I'm fine.
What's the problem, guys?
I thought you were
gonna teach us a lesson.
You weren't good
enough for Disaster
and you're not good
enough to beat us.
Tasuku, over there.
What could that be?
♪
(yelling)
I cast Blue Dragon Shield.
Well played.
End of move.
Gao managed to
destroy two monsters
but he was unable
to cause any damage
to Kyoya at all!
With Blue Dragon
Shield's ability,
Kyoya's gauge
increases to four
and it's now his turn!
Not looking good, kid.
We've got four life
points to his six.
I hope you've got
some kind of plan.
Don't worry,
we just made him
use up all the
cards in his hand.
What makes
you think that?
I'm impressed, Gremlin.
Enabling me to
draw this card
just when I need it.
I Buddy Call!
(screams)
The living curse that
unites all abominations.
The king of evil dragons,
burning thousands
of souls to ash.
Demonic Demise Dragon,
Azi Dahaka!
(gasping)
It's the most terrifying
thing I've ever seen!
What is it?
My name is Azi Dahaka.
Long have I waited
for this moment.
Those who know the truth
have summoned me here.
None can stand before me.
And none will come after me.
Fear me!
Dread me!
There's no escape!
Erasure of history!
(shouting)
He's able to attack all
of the opponent's monsters
at the same time?
Drum, Dagger,
what's happening?
(Gao yells)
Not just the monsters,
but the fighter, too!
And items.
What chance does anyone have?
How ill mannered.
I've never seen
anything so powerful.
We can't afford to
lose any more time.
‐You ready?
‐Let's do it.
Hey, Jackknife,
unfold first move!
Become one
with the lightning
and strike him down
with your power!
Reveal Jackknife
Thunder Storm!
(thunder booming)
I cast Power of Mythology!
You'll be a myth too
if you don't move it!
Whoa, let's book it!
Right behind you!
Glacier's crush!
♪
Thunder reigns!
(shouting)
This is your fault!
I'll get you
for this, Shido!
We'd better hurry.
Yeah.
Ugh!
No, Kiri!
♪
You can't run from me.
I wondered where
she was hiding.
This is getting bad.
And it gets worse.
To what do we owe
the pleasure, Rouga?
I thought you'd be
miles away by now.
I would leave, but something
keeps calling me back.
Did someone catch the
license plate on that truck?
Azi Dahaka has 10,000
power and defense.
He can attack an opponent
and all of their monsters
on the field.
And he destroys items
whenever he does damage.
Kyoya's power is seriously
out of this world.
And his Buddy is
beyond all conventions.
If you're looking for
someone unconventional,
look no further.
You can't get
more unconventional
than this bonehead
who's down to one life,
but still thinks
he's gonna win.
Thanks, I think.
That's why I chose you.
Don't change
for anyone, kid.
Now let's blow open
the walls of this place.
All right, I call Systemic
Dagger to the center.
Thank you for the chance
to redeem my honor.
And Boomerang
Dragon to the left!
I'm the thunder
from down under!
I chose to evolve Drum!
Get ready, 'cause
Super Armordragon,
Drum Breaker Dragon
is in the house!
Drum and Dagger, do a
link attack on Azi Dahaka.
Only a fool would
dare to ignite my wrath!
Danse Macabre!
Drill Ram Breaker!
Their combined attack
comes to exactly 10,000!
‐Now break!
Anyone for a
little penetrate?
♪
If I am destroyed,
the world will end.
What?
The instant that I vanish,
my destiny will be realized.
I forewarned all
of you, did I not?
None can stand before me.
And none will come after me.
(roaring)
Gao did it!
Gao destroyed the
colossal size four monster,
Azi Dahaka!
(snickering)
You couldn't have known,
but you just did
me a big favor.
(ground trembling)
(gasping)
(screams)
What is this?
Haven't you caused
enough damage already?
I've been wanting
to try this out
for as long as
I can remember.
Equip.
Demonic Demise Sword,
Aqulta Gwaneff.
(gasps)
What's wrong, Tasuku?
I just got
a bad feeling.
There's no
turning back now.
♪
(lightning striking)
(murmuring)
♪
Demonic Demise Sword.
Aqulta Gwaneff.
I owe it all to you.
The Sword of Truth
can only be equipped
after Azi Dahaka's
been defeated.
There's more‐‐with
Dragon Throne's ability,
that sword can't be destroyed
or returned to his hand.
Talk about intense.
How is this possible?
Well, it is.
You know why?
Because I decided
that it should be.
The rules of this world,
its law and order,
everything's
determined by me.
By me, I tell you.
For I am Master Kyoya Gaen.
It's time for...
Tasuku and Gao's
‐Card of the Day.
Today we're gonna talk about
the strongest
dragon of them all,
Demonic Demise Dragon,
Azi Dahaka.
It's a ginormous
size four monster.
You can only call
him if you've got
his exclusive set
spell, Dragon Throne.
But once he's in action...
He's able to attack all
of an opponent's monsters
and the fighter
in just one move.
And if he causes damage,
he'll destroy
your item, too!
So what do
you think, guys?
Think you can
open up one of these?
‐You'll never know
‐until you try.
♪
Hey, Gao, you remember
the day we became Buddies?
Have we ever
been through a lot
of tough battles
since then, huh, kid?
Well, there's
one more to go.
It's the last showdown.
Break to the Future.
Get ready for the
best Buddyfight ever!