♪
Get ready for a
cool new card game
that connects to
a parallel universe.
Special cards
act as portals
bringing monsters to Earth
to become buddies with humans,
and through friendship
and courage,
help them take
on fight challenges.
It's called Buddyfight!
♪
Dragon Vanquishing
Sword, Balmung!
What's the deal
with that sword, yo?
It's basically a
magic dragon eraser.
Special properties
in the steel
let the user destroy
them with just one blow.
Cha‐ching, how do
I get one of those?
♪
(whimpers)
Hey, why so sad?
♪
He's really upset
about that card.
Win.
Not...
So if he didn't put the
card in his deck, who did?
Don't know.
Unless.
Hey!
You gave it to him,
didn't you, Rouga?
♪
Winning a match
with a hate card
doesn't automatically make
you some kind of magician.
Am I right?
Never good to
be hatin', yo.
If winning's all
you care about,
I can see why you
would use them.
What do you think, Z?
Would you use 'em if it
was the only way to win?
Maybe, if it
was the only way.
Nin.
That's it, I'm going next.
‐Why you‐‐
‐Huh?
I don't usually get angry,
but when I do, it's
for a good reason!
Good or bad, these hate cards
are messing with the fun.
No way!
This isn't the
Buddyfight I know!
♪
Kemura was
always all alone.
♪
Kem!
(laughing)
Hello, there!
I'm Sylph,
the fairy.
‐Ribbit.
‐Huh? Wait!
Don't tell me you're
supposed to be my buddy!
I'm not sure about this.
I know quirky's the new black,
but this is a lot to take on.
Then again, you could be
a diamond in the rough.
Okay, rule number one!
That was first time
Kemura meet Sylph.
I wasn't 100% excited
to be his buddy,
but then,
something happened.
(buzzing)
(Sylph screaming)
Let me outta here!
You don't listen
so good, huh?
It didn't take long for his true
character to shine through.
(straining)
Ever since, Kemura and
I have been best friends.
He's funny, and cool
and majorly strong,
and I didn't
think so at first,
but he actually
listens to me.
Sylph only one
who talk to Kemura.
Being her friend
all I care about.
♪
Until Rouga
show up, ribbit.
(screams)
Here comes Drill Bunker!
♪
Rouga help to
learn Buddyfight.
Kemura think to
get really strong
and get more friends,
so work hard.
♪
But Kemura go too far.
And make bad mistake.
Betray Genma.
Hurt good friend.
♪
Kemura feel bad, Kem.
Hey, Kem‐Kem!
I'm talking to you!
♪
‐You up for a fight?
‐Ill‐mannered mongrel!
Respond, please!
Ribbit?
Huh? You're
feeling better!
One of these
days, mister!
So, what do you
say, huh, Kem‐Kem?
Huh?
She's growing on me.
‐She's okay
‐Yeah.
I hope she wins.
Kiri's all alone
out there.
Don't worry, I'm
sure he's all right.
Is that girl serious?
Kemura's just
revealed all his cards.
He's the perfect target
to be hate carded now.
There's no way he's foolish
enough to accept her challenge.
I don't know.
He looks like he's pretty
into it, I'd say.
Oh?
You know him best, Rouga.
What do you think?
I never taught him to play
like that, but he did win.
Just let him do
what he wants.
That girl, I've
never seen her play.
Will she be able to win?
If she plays
her cards right.
We can't afford
to have any more losses.
You see her fight, Gao?
‐She's good.
‐She's wicked strong.
She just might be the best
fighter out of all of us.
‐Uh‐huh.
‐Oh.
Let's see her break
it down already.
All we can do is
hope for the best.
Kazane, we're
counting on you.
Do it for Kiri.
It looks like both teams have
chosen their next fighters.
A kaleidoscope of
excitement and adventure!
Luminize!
Kaleido Labyrinth!
Luminize, Wydar Sarkal.
Buddy skill on.
♪
It's feathers versus
fairy dust for the win!
Buddyfight!
(screeching)
(screams)
End of move.
Kemura's slow
out of the gate
with only one damage
point on his first turn.
Let's see what Kazane's
got to answer that!
Hmm, so that's how it is!
What gives?
Even with a bad hand, one
point's pretty weak, bro.
Maybe he's making mistakes cause
he's tired from his last fight.
He looks fine.
That's weird.
Is he making up for
what he did to Genma?
What are you saying?
That he's losing on purpose?
How we make a comeback
without keeping it real, yo?
Hey, man, got
a question for ya.
Remember when I had
that one turn victory
against our friend Rouga?
Like it was
yesterday, dog!
Well, just like
hate cards,
those kind of games
can get your opponents
really bummed
out and stuff.
Unless you're the
thick‐skinned demon type.
You're the
sensitive demon type.
Kemura, listen to me!
I get how you feel
about all this.
And I know you want
to make up for it,
but trust me, this
really isn't the way!
You always give your opponent
your best fight, so bring it!
Someone's worked up.
Don't listen to him.
But he right.
Kemura not give best.
Ready or not, draw!
Charge and draw!
I call Fledgling Warrior,
Ocker Glaser to the center.
Gummy Slime to the left,
and Scout, Criticizing Kiwa
to the right!
♪
And for something
completely different,
Mission Card
"Defeat Monsters!"
A mission card's a
special set spell
that gives you a bonus if you
fulfill certain requirements
and you guessed it,
these are called missions.
That's weird.
I've never
heard of that one.
You don't get
out much, do you?
The bonus for
"Defeat Monsters!"
lets you add two
cards to your hand
if you can complete
the whole mission.
But it's definitely
not easy to do.
Kazane has to destroy two of
Kemura's monsters for this one.
Ocker and Kiwa, alright, boys,
link attack Vaverudorahhe!
Kemura, come on!
‐Let's get him!
‐Yeah!
(yelling)
We're like
human weed eaters!
I think a little slash
and burn will do the trick!
One monster down
and one to go!
And with Ocker Glaser's
ability to penetrate,
Kemura's life
points drop to nine.
Kuguru, does Legend World
have any counter spells
like Drago Energy or
is this as cool as it gets?
Well, the enhance card,
the Wydar Sarkal,
is pretty similar
to a counter spell.
Why do you ask?
Man, that Kazane.
She's awesome!
What's all the fuss?
She just used a link attack.
Ocker could defeat that
Venus flytrap on his own,
but she's thinking
strategy all the way.
Explain, please.
It's like this, bro.
If Kazane had only
attacked with the Ocker,
Kemura could have
cast the Wyder Sarkal
hitting her with a counter,
so with the link attack,
she protects her unit and
guarantees taking his out.
That girl's way ahead
of the game, you heard!
She's giving it everything
she's got out there!
I hope Kemura starts
doing the same.
Okay, Gummy Slime,
go attack Kem‐Kem!
Gummy, gummy!
♪
End of move.
It doesn't look like
he's really even trying.
He'd better pick it up or
he'll be hitting the showers.
Your move.
‐This bad.
‐So do something!
Hmm!
Not feel good.
Kemura hurt Genma
when try for winning.
Hmm.
But you won just
like you wanted.
Yeah, and it bad not to
give best in fight, yes?
But can't stop thinking.
Kemura not want
to hurt anyone else.
Never.
So confused.
Not know what to do.
(cries)
What's the hold up?
He's not even attempting
to draw his cards.
Fairy got your
tongue or something?
(crowd jeering)
Yes, Kem.
No, Kem.
I wonder why he's
just standing there.
Typical Kemura.
Guess he's getting cold
feet again like always.
Ask Rouga.
He's his star
pupil after all.
Hmm?
He's not here.
(inhales deeply)
Kemura!
Huh?
I‐‐
He never says
people's names.
That's a first.
Crazy.
♪
Win this!
Come on, start trying!
Rouga care what
happen to Kemura?
Listen up!
Stop this.
Victory can be yours.
But you must use
all your strength!
♪
All my strength,
then win, Kem.
Kemura will do that.
Alright, now
you're talking!
I don't know what
that delay was
but he's finally
drawing his cards.
♪
Looks like he's
actually gonna try.
Rouga has a way of changing
people's minds for them, bro.
Judging by these waves,
he's getting ready.
None of this
makes any sense.
If Rouga can just talk
people into winning,
why'd he have to give
Kemura that hate card?
It's so pointless.
Watch out, Kemura
fight with full power.
Winning fair and
square, using own cards,
make up for
hurting friend, Genma.
I call to center
King of Forest, Zlatorog.
(roaring)
♪
Vaverudorahhe, go attack
that Ocker guy, Kem.
(screeching)
Poetic justice.
Now, Zlatorog, attack
the fighter, Kem.
(roars)
(yells)
End of move.
Yeah, that's
more like it!
By the way,
I'm Kazane!
Huh?
I'm also known as Wind.
‐That's my nickname.
‐Ribbit?
What?
Now are we gonna
talk or fight?
I don't know what your story
is or what makes you tick,
but I'm so happy to
have an equal opponent.
Call to the center,
go Gummy Slime!
Gummy, gummy!
See?
I know that the hate card
was not your idea.
♪
Divide and conquer
with my Whip of Destiny!
So just put it behind you and
from now on, fight your own way.
Ah.
By destroying the
second monster,
Kazane has
fulfilled her mission.
The deck spell worked
like a charm
adding two cards
to her hand.
Huh?
What makes you think you know
anything about my Kemura anyway?
(Sylph yells)
The way someone
fights says a lot.
♪
Just worry about
winning your match, missy!
You talk big for someone
who's a pint‐sized fairy.
Center Gummy Slime,
attack the fighter.
Gummy, gummy, gummy!
I can tell me and Kem‐Kem
would be fast friends
after hashing it out.
Fast friends, no!
I'm the only friend
he has or will ever need.
It figures.
What is it with princesses
and frogs, huh?
Look who brought the drama.
I'm sorry, but
I can't watch.
You girls are weird.
Gummy, gummy!
End of move.
Get up!
You can't let her
get the best of you.
Make this turn count!
That's it, let her have it!
Call to left, Kem.
Cuelebre!
We need all the help
we can get out there.
‐So, put me in!
‐Good idea.
Buddy call Sylph
to center, Kem.
♪
Leave it to me!
I'll protect you and put
that girl in her place.
‐Hmm.
‐Something funny?
Nothing.
I'm just wondering,
were you the one
that sent that hate card
into Kem‐Kem's deck
without him
knowing about it?
Of all the nerve!
It wasn't me!
Raremaro acted alone.
‐I thought so.
‐It was him?
Of course!
That's why Rouga was
so angry about it.
That little winged
bug needs to shush.
She's in trouble.
Raremaro's one of the four
Demon Generals, right?
So, is he a good
friend of yours?
School classmate, Kem.
Either way, if someone does
something you don't like,
you have to tell them.
How do that, Kem?
Walk up to him and tell him how
you feel about what he did.
He not be mad?
Maybe, but he's
the one who's wrong.
If he's your real
friend, he'll apologize
and hopefully do his
best to make up for it.
Thank you, Kem.
Cast Decree of Dullahan!
♪
(roaring)
Watch out, girlfriend!
Kemura casts the
powerful Decree of Dullahan.
All of the Wydar Sarkal now have
the ability for a double attack.
It's not looking
good for her, bro.
His monsters are
already pretty choice.
It'll be tough to beat him
now with that second wave.
Maybe we should
have just let him
throw the match
in our favor.
No, win or lose,
we bring our best game.
Don't you dare
forget it, man!
Kemura give
everything, Kem.
I should hope so.
Cuelebre, attack monster
in the center!
(shrieks)
And penetrate, Kem.
(yells)
And now, double attack.
I cast Divine Protection
of Shalsana!
With that counter spell,
a player pays one gauge
to nullify an
opponent's attack,
while at the same time,
regaining one life point.
Ribbit.
Kemura change
strategy, Kem.
Send Vaverudorahhe
and then attack left.
Gummy!
Why is he diverting
his attention
from attacking
that girl?
Uh, cause
there's no point?
Because of the card
she just played.
Yeah, he couldn't knock
her life points down to zero
even if all his
monsters joined up.
So, he switched his assault
to the two units
on the sides instead.
A smart play.
I wasn't aware Kemura
was such a good fighter.
And getting
better every day.
But having a great teacher
is half the battle.
What's surprising is that
Aragami saw his potential
when none of us did.
(screams)
What a burn!
Why do you always have that
happy look on your face?
This is fun, isn't it?
I can change that!
(yells)
End of move.
He's gaining
the upper hand?
This is an
awesome fight!
Looking good, Kemura!
Now finish it.
Not bad, Frog Boy!
‐Nice move.
‐Kemura's amazing.
You can do this.
Huh?
What?
Giving your best
is fun, eh, Kem‐Kem?
You're really
good, you know.
Thanks.
This is getting me
all revved up.
I want to fight too now.
Not me, I'm hungry.
I'm so pumped, I want
to play her too, yo.
For a non‐demon, yeah,
she's pretty wicked.
Okay, my turn again.
Get a load of me.
Charge and draw!
It's time for
a buddy call.
Me ready.
Blade Wing Phoenix
to the right position.
Mimic with a Prize
to the left,
and I discard one card from
my hand and equip Gloryseeker!
(screaming)
Ribbit!
♪
Girl power!
With that, Kemura's
down to one life point.
Must win.
Blade, go get our
new friend, Kem‐Kem.
♪
Not yet.
Me cast Holy Grail!
He just blocked the attack.
Bet he forgot Blade
has a double attack.
That's what
she's banking on.
She's so fly.
(screaming)
‐Yeah!
‐Game over.
Winner: Kazane Fujimiya.
Incredible!
Aibo is now
on the board!
But we still
need four more wins
to complete our mission
and get Kiri back.
(crying)
We really lost.
That match was
totally cool.
Now we're friends, we
should play again sometime.
You got it, Kem.
Whoever fights
next has to win.
Understand?
Kemura grateful
to Rouga, Kem.
Hmm?
Because you teach me how
to Buddyfight good, Kem,
Kemura now can make
some good friends.
Hmmph!
Win or lose,
he's never happy.
Raremaro!
If you want put card
in Kemura's deck,
you have to tell
first, Kem.
What he said!
Okay, but I only did it
for you to help you win.
Do that again,
Kemura never forgive you!
(yelps)
(laughing)
Hey, Kem‐Kem!
Come on, why don't
we fight again?
Right now!
‐Can't.
‐Huh?
Sorry, someone else Kemura
need to fight first, Kem.
You're right.
That's a good call.
♪
Where do you think
he's going in such a hurry?
Into the mountains
would be my best guess.
Yeah, he's gonna go
make peace with Genma, yo.
Nice.
(grunting)
I wonder if Genma
will forgive him.
Huh?
Sure he will.
Huh.
That's what friends do, man, and
they've been best buds for ages.
♪
I wonder who the
fighters are gonna be
for the fourth match
of this showdown.
I'll go!
You ain't seen
nothing yet!
Hey, nobody
likes a game hog.
I'll fight next.
We saw you fight already.
It's time for someone else
to have a turn like me.
Ill‐mannered!
I guess you're right.
You got revved up watching
Kazane's match too, huh?
Nuh‐uh!
Don't forget, we can't afford
to lose a single match now.
That's enough
motivation for me.
It's time we showed them
how good Aibo really is.
Come on, guys,
it's go time!
Yeah, right on.
Nin.
It's time for...
Tasuku and Gao's...
‐Card of the Day!
Today's card is
Bladewing Phoenix.
Hey, I've met him.
He's Kazane's buddy and comes
all the way from Dungeon World.
Bladewing's got 5,000 power, two
critical and a double attack.
That's rare for
a Size Two monster.
All in all, he's a great
choice to have your back.
As long as you don't mind
Bladewing nagging you
about your manners.
So, what do
you think, guys?
You think you
can open one of these?
You'll never
know until you try!
♪
Next time it's Zanya
against Kanahebi,
and things get
a little ugly
when we find out
there's a dark history
between the two of them.
Next episode,
"Flying Ninja Showdown!"
It's gonna be
super stealth!