♪
Get ready for a
cool new card game
that connects to a
parallel universe.
Special cards act as portals,
bringing monsters to Earth
to become buddies with humans,
and through
friendship and courage,
help them take
on fight challenges.
It's called Buddyfight!
♪
I don't see how some little
stone slab's gonna help me.
But what're you
gonna do, am I right?
Ancient tablet,
please be awesome!
♪
I'm Legendary Brave, Tasuku.
Get 'em, Craftsman, Baku.
Sage, Kuguru.
And I'm Dancing
Magician, Tetsuya, yo.
How about a formation?
Baku to the right,
Tetsuya to the left,
and Legendary Brave, Tasuku,
I need you in the center.
‐But I wanna be in the center.
‐Fine.
Take my spot, I'll
shift to the left.
Link attack with Tasuku
and protect the center.
Kuguru, keep speed‐reading
till you find some pointers.
‐I understand.
‐All for one and one for all!
♪
Hi, Kazane.
Maybe you'd consider
fighting me next.
‐What do you say?
‐Go, Gao‐ao.
I don't know, who are you?
This is most rude, young
man, introduce yourself.
I'm the Mighty Sun Fighter.
It's Mikado, Gao Mikado!
♪
I forbid it, we don't
know anything about him.
Hey, nice to meet you,
sure I'll take you on.
Am I invisible?
A kaleidoscope of
excitement and adventure.
Luminize, Kaleido Labyrinth.
‐Let's go!
‐I have my eye on you!
So no shenanigans or
you'll be answering to me.
You hear that, mister?
Showering the sky with
Scorching Sun Rockets.
Soleil Dragon Deck, luminize!
Buddyfight!
‐Let's raise the flag.
I fight for Dungeon World.
♪
And I fight for Dragon World.
‐You can go first.
‐For real?
You wanna play this
one without your Buddy?
Drum had some things to take
care of, but don't worry,
I'm sure he'll be
here when it counts.
I'll be flying solo
till he shows.
I wanted a duet.
Suit yourself.
First I Charge, then I'll Draw.
Watch out, here I come!
I'm gonna cast Dangerous Fuse.
♪
I love Dungeon World, 'cause
it's a game within a game.
Right, now, pop quiz time.
Which of these two cards is
Divine Protection of Shalsana?
If you're right, the
card's added to my hand.
If you're wrong, both of 'em
will be set to my gauge.
Basically you're saying that
you can't lose either way.
‐That's one awesome card.
‐Stop complimenting her game.
She's your opponent, figure
out how to prevent her
from adding more
cards to her hand.
I have to say, the
dudette's got game.
That one, on the right.
Ugh, you picked
Bladewing Phoenix.
‐Oh yeah!
‐Nice guess, you got lucky,
but we're just getting
started, there'll be more.
For now, I call to
the center Gummy Slime.
‐Gummy, Gummy‐my‐my.
‐Attack!
‐I'm gonna cast Dragon Breath!
‐Gummy‐my‐my?
‐End of move.
‐Oh, yikes!
‐He got my Gummy!
‐Your move.
My turn for some fun.
Draw!
Charge and Draw!
I call to the right
Thunderknights, Halberd Dragon!
And to the left position I
call Systemic Dagger Dragon!
On your command.
(roaring)
You're gonna leave
your center wide open?
I equip Steel Fist,
Dragoknuckle.
Halberd and Dagger, come on,
let's form a united front!
Let's go!
(screaming)
Danse Macabre!
That's not all, Steel
Fist, Dragoknuckle!
(shouting)
‐End of move.
‐Six damage points at once?
He's way better than
I thought he was.
He's the best fighter
I've seen in ages.
‐I really gotta step it up.
‐Your move.
Get up, counter attack!
I just thought of
something that might work!
This game's getting exciting.
That didn't even phase her.
Bro stood me up.
So he can't be mad if
I eat his food, right?
‐Mhm.
‐If I know Gao,
he probably went looking
for Drum already.
Yeah, he said there's a totally
cool Buddyfight going on
right now at Castle, hurry up!
‐That sounds like Gao to me.
‐Uh‐huh.
Let's go find him.
Charge and Draw!
Yeah, okay.
Let's have a do‐over.
Dangerous Fuse.
Name that card, which
one is Gummy Slime?
‐The one on the left.
‐Ding‐ding, that's correct.
That gives her six cards,
and Gao's only got
three in his hand.
I guess this dude's
finally met his match.
Come on, Gao‐ao, you can do it.
I'm gonna cast
Cecilia's Spell Disarm.
Hey, what is that?
Oh yeah, I'd say that
was a pretty good cast.
That card can destroy any
set spell or item card.
You really know your stuff,
but it's still gonna cost
her two gauge to use it.
I call Mimic with a Prize,
Fledgling Warrior,
Ocker Glaser, and Gummy Slime!
Let's show this Sun Fighter
what our world's about.
‐Gummy‐my, Gummy!
‐Yeah!
‐Halberd!
‐I'm stuck, master!
Agh, let go!
Get off of‐‐
(muffled remarks)
That's good luck for you!
End of move.
Did Gao really lose five
life points in one turn?
Gummy Slime's like glue,
it prevents you from moving.
He really should've
studied up
about Dungeon World
before he started this.
‐Talk about losing face.
‐And on top of it,
that girl's a natural born
Dungeon World fighter.
Not like me, I'm not
a natural at anything.
This is such an epic world.
It's got tons of twists
and turns and stuff!
Right, I love it,
it's totally crazy
not knowing what's
gonna happen next!
Not just that, I chose it
'cause I see some real potential
in it, you know, like a way
to make tons of new friends.
That's a really awesome reason!
Huh?
You can add me as
a friend for sure!
Thanks, it's great
to meet other people
who like to play
for the fun of it.
I'll be up to 100 in no time!
The challenge
doesn't scare them.
I wish I was brave.
Help me out, Dagger, go take
care of that Gummy Slime!
(growling and whimpering)
‐Lunch!
‐Gummy‐my‐my.
Gummy‐my‐my, Gummy‐my‐my.
Gummy‐my‐my!
Halberd, attack Mimic!
♪
Mimic.
Mimic with a Prize is
a pretty fun card to use.
Whenever it's destroyed we both
have to check the top card
in our decks, and as long
as it's not a monster,
then you're golden.
I get back one life point.
And what if it
is a monster card?
Ah, Thousand Rapier.
You receive one damage point.
‐What a burn!
‐End of move.
But what if your card
had been a monster?
I would've suffered
one point of damage too.
So it's kinda like a
game of chance then.
‐That sounds fair.
‐Whether you're lucky or not,
if you want something you
should go out and take it.
So basically we
create our own luck.
‐Exactly!
‐What a kook.
Chatting all
friendly‐like with her?
If he's not careful, he
could lose the entire match.
You ready to go down the
rabbit hole again, my friend?
I draw, Charge and Draw.
I cast Pillar of Fire.
Destroy Halberd Dragon.
(groaning)
I'm toast.
Way to take my Halberd!
Man, Kazane.
Your strategy's so nonstop
that I haven't been
able to do anything.
From deep within the labyrinth,
I call the fierce fanatic
of terror and despair
to the center!
Say hello to Thunder Spartis.
Now attack the fighter.
Thunder grovel!
(grunting)
Uh‐oh, Gao‐ao's only
got one life point left.
Ready for more?
Let's go Ocker Glaser.
Attack our friend
the Sun Fighter.
Hee‐yah, hee‐yah.
‐To adventure!
‐Stop right there!
I cast Blue Dragon Shield!
End of move.
(gasping)
So close, I almost got him too!
‐Well, next time.
‐She's bossing the game.
I know, and to make things
worse, her center monster,
Thunder Spartis,
has 9,000 defense.
Systemic Dagger's
power's only 3,000,
so Gao needs to find at
least 6,000 more power
from somewhere and
do a link attack.
It's the only way
bro can win now.
Let's see how he
deals with this.
Drum Bunker Dragon.
Where are ya, pal?
I could kinda use
your help right now.
♪
I call to the center
Drum Bunker Dragon.
Buddy Call!
♪
Drum Bunker Dragon,
son of Fang Slade
Terrestrial XIII.
♪
Version 2.0.
My Buddy to the rescue!
I thought you'd never make it!
Guess you started
to miss me, huh?
Let me guess, he's
your Buddy Monster?
You got it, he's my
main man‐‐main dragon.
It's great to have
you back, Drum.
Hey, let's save the mushy
stuff till later, 'kay, kid?
First, you and me got a hole
to dig ourselves out of.
Now you're here
I know what to do.
Link attack on Thunder Spartis,
and for a 3,000 power boost
I cast Dragoenergy on Drum!
This is a new one for me.
‐You got my back, right?
‐Yeah!
♪
‐End of move.
‐Outrageous!
Statistically, I didn't
think he could do it.
What a beast, you're
like a new dragon!
That was nothing, I'm
just getting started.
‐Your move.
‐I gotta admit,
nobody's ever taken down
my Spartis that easy.
I know I'm stating the obvious,
but your buddy's rockin' it.
‐That's right!
‐Draw.
But Blade's real impressive too.
Prepare to be
razzled and dazzled.
I Buddy Call the great
Bladewing Phoenix to the left.
About time I get to
ruffle some feathers!
Circle in on your
prey, attack Drum!
I wonder what this
birdie's deal is.
Release Raptor Blades!
♪
You'll need more than
that to defeat me!
Okay, do it again.
He's got a double attack.
My encore, Raptor Blades!
(grunting)
I did my part, kid.
You gotta finish the job.
Yeah!
Oh, honestly,
I can't come between those two.
Ocker Glaser, we
can't let up now!
A party, mind if I Ocker‐crash?
‐Agh!
‐End of move.
That was close, if not for that
Buddy Gift it would be all over.
Like I said, Dungeon
World's unpredictable.
Like snowboarding down
an avalanche or something.
I call to the center
Double Sword Dragon,
and to the right,
Thousand Rapier Dragon.
Thousand, you first,
attack Kazane!
Right, in vero veritas!
Keep it going, Dagger!
I cast the Pillar of Fire!
(yelling)
It's up to you, Double Sword.
Help that Bladewing
Phoenix burn itself up.
(screaming)
(growling)
♪
‐I will reunite!
‐End of move.
‐You got my blade!
‐Yes, I did.
‐Your move.
‐Draw.
Huh, hm.
I call to the center
Mimic with a Prize!
Now attack Double Sword Dragon!
Bleccch, blech!
(shouting)
Come on, Glaser, let's really
freak him out, all right?
Yeah!
To adventure!
I cast White Dragon Shield!
End of move.
Well played, Mr. Sun Fighter.
Just one life point left.
Gao has to win it
all in this turn.
I hear that, but he
can't attack the fighter
until he defeats Mimic first.
And if he does
manage to destroy it,
then each of them has
to check their top card.
The outcome hangs on it,
if the card's a monster
then he receives one damage
point automatically.
She chose a good one, I
can't think of a better card
to call to the center
at this point.
I have to defeat Mimic
if I stand any chance
of winning this one.
Thousand, it's all
in your hands now!
Teach 'em not to
stick his tongue out!
En garde, dungeon pest.
(gurgling noises)
So what's it gonna be this time?
Bonus, a spell!
I regain one life point.
So which is it?
Item, spell, or kablooey?
Please, not a monster.
Well, come on, don't
leave us in suspense.
It's an item card, I get
another life point too!
(shouting and sighing)
Time for the final phase!
I cast!
♪
Impact!
Gargantua Punisher!
♪
Guess you can't win 'em all.
(screaming)
♪
Game over.
Winner, Gao Mikado.
All right!
‐I sent 'em back to the dungeon.
‐Nice!
‐He did it!
‐Sweetness.
I wish he wouldn't
scare me like that.
‐Hey, where's Kiri?
‐Uh...
I almost had you there, huh?
I don't know about that,
but it sure wasn't boring.
These kind of fights are
exciting for the spectators too.
‐Yeah!
‐If people watch my fights
and then challenge me
to a game like you did,
then I'll totally be
able to make 100 friends.
It worked on me, 99 more to go.
I bet that you've
got a ton of friends,
being such a great
fighter and all.
You know something, I do.
Because of this game,
I know a lot more people.
If I wasn't competing in
Buddyfights I might never
have talked to them or even
met 'em in the first place.
Just like you, I hope to
befriend all my opponents.
Maybe even Rouga.
Someday.
Who is this Rouga?
‐Nah, never mind.
‐Come on, tell me!
‐I don't wanna!
‐Yes, you do, spill it.
‐You look pretty tasty.
‐I do not!
In Dungeon World, we lock
up scoundrels like you.
I'll never be able to fight
as well as those guys.
Gao and the others are always
at least 10 steps ahead of me.
♪
(yelling)
Game over, winner,
Tetsuya Kurodake.
♪
I bet one day they'll get tired
of me always tagging along.
♪
It's not like I'll
ever be as good
at Buddyfighting as they are.
No matter who you fight,
do what you must to win.
That's what will
make you stronger.
Trust me.
You mean, if I try hard
even I can get good?
Of course, just remember
this, the only thing
of any value in this
world is winning.
Maybe I should start taking
Rouga's advice more seriously.
♪
(whimpering)
No more losing!
(gasping)
I'm just in time.
Looks like you'd do anything
to start winning, huh?
Uh, yeah, I guess I would.
♪
(howling noise)
(screaming)
Isn't that Kiri?
This looks great.
(chewing noisily)
‐It's delicious.
‐You know it.
My grandma should start
her own restaurant.
It's gotta be the greatest
food on the planet.
Yeah, she totally should!
Thanks for having me over!
So Tets, where were
you today, bro?
You missed a great match.
We were recording in the studio.
Finally found the time to lay
down some righteous new tracks.
Yeah, wait till you hear
my new rap, it's ace.
Almost as good as these eats!
Hm, ah!
(grunting)
I can't hold on any longer!
'Sup, Akatsuki, were you
getting hungry up there?
Wow, you must be psychic.
(chewing noisily)
‐Oh, they're so delicious!
‐We aim to please!
Anyway, what's Zanya's
little brother doing here?
He's a ninja, so you're
probably spying on us, right?
That's not it, and in
case you're wondering,
I'm sure not hiding from Z's
majorly brutal training session
‐or anything.
‐Tell the truth, Akatsuki.
‐The kid's hiding, isn't he?
‐Yup, no doubt about it.
Tets used to bail on me too.
Why you gotta be
hating on me, yo?
Akatsuki!
'Sup, Zanya?
It's not what you think.
I just came over to
ask for a little help
with my algebra homework,
and, uh‐‐not the ear!
Please let go, please!
‐Ohhh.
‐We're leaving.
‐Why don't you come in?
‐How about you take a break
from practice and
just chill here?
I am kinda hungry, but I'm
allergic to girls‐‐food.
Don't worry, we can work it out.
Hey, I just realized
Kiri's not here.
Where'd he go after Castle?
‐Beats me.
‐I would've invited him,
but I didn't notice
him leaving the match.
‐Hmm.
‐Hey, I know!
Let me show you what I
picked up in my training.
It'll blow your mind.
What do you mean by picked up?
(gasping)
♪
In Dungeon World, I got
this wicked new weapon
and a new look,
what do you think?
Wow, you look awesome!
Tell me all about Dungeon World!
No lie, I took down a giant,
with the help of
some weirdos I met.
Hey, Gao!
There's trouble, help!
‐A girl?
‐Paruko?
She's kinda stealing my thunder.
Kiri was just carried away
by Rouga and some monster!
‐What?
Tell me everything
so we can find him!
♪
And then what?
Uh, nothing, but I've got
Takosuke following them.
(phone ringing)
That's him now.
Hey, what's happening?
Okay, I see.
What, no way!
What flavor, really?
And then‐‐uh‐huh, oh dear.
And now?
Say what, they just
arrived at where?
Sengoku Academy?
‐Sengoku?
‐Academy?
♪
Hello there, I'm Paruko Nanana,
your guide to the
Buddyfight world.
You saw Kazane use the card
Mimic with a Prize
from Dungeon World.
What's the prize, you ask?
Well, when this monster
is destroyed, both players
have to check the top
card in their decks.
If that card is anything
except for a monster,
you get back one life point!
But if it is a monster,
you get one point of damage.
As usual, Gao got
lucky out there.
Can you open a Buddy Rare
card, what do you think?
♪
Next time, we head to Sengoku
Academy to get Kiri back,
but we stumble into a
Buddyfight underworld.
What are Rouga and his
demon generals up to?
Next episode, Buddyfight
Intensified, Sengoku Academy!
It's gonna be a scorcher!