♪
Get ready for a
cool new card game
that connects to
a parallel universe.
Special cards
act as portals,
bringing
monsters to Earth
to become
buddies with humans.
And through
friendship and courage,
help them take on
fight challenges.
It's called
Buddyfight.
As you know,
it's a unique card.
And I'd really like
to see you master it.
Uh.
Hmm.
♪
Huh?
The special rare Gargantua
Punisher card is all yours.
(murmuring)
There's something else,
this card evolves.
Huh?
In order to manifest
its full power,
Gargantua Punisher
splits into four.
As you gain experience
with each Buddyfight,
you'll discover
the true power of this card.
Awesome.
But you know,
I wouldn't feel right
unless I gave you something
in return, Tasuku.
Here, take this.
Dragonblade, Dragobrave?
But that's not even
close to a fair trade.
The only reason I beat you
is 'cause of this card.
So I figure it
kind of makes sense
for you to have it.
Thanks a lot, Gao.
I'll remember our fight
when I use it.
Hah.
♪
Good morning, humans.
Are you up for some fun?
Yeah, we sure are!
It's time for hip hop
class with Demon Asmodai.
That's the guy
from Magic World.
Monsters sure are
popular these days, huh?
I read he got into
show biz through Magic World.
I guess we're going to see
lots more of them on TV.
Asmodai's dance show
is the best, I love it!
Please.
Let's begin with
a simple warm up.
♪
Moonwalk.
‐Moonwalk.
Last one,
do the backward cobra.
(groaning)
Now wrap your tail
around your head.
(groaning)
This is a real
piece of cake.
Easy for you to say.
I don't have a tail.
Of course not, silly.
I'd be worried if you did.
‐Can't hold it!
(crashing)
Ha ha, sorry if it was
too tough for you humans.
But I bet you got
a good stretch, huh?
Now remember,
keep movin' and groovin'
and one day you might
be as famous as me.
Breakfast's ready.
Dancing with a Demon!
Man, what a feast!
Is it someone's
birthday or somethin'?
I'm starving.
(whooshing)
I made all this for Drum!
Huh, for me?
Yes, since I didn't
know what you really like,
I thought I'd cook up
a few of my specialties.
I gotta tell you, Drum,
you really
surprised us yesterday.
♪
Aaah!
What was that,
my mouth's burning!
Here you go,
drink some water.
My boss didn't believe me
when I told him there'd
been a fire breathing dragon
on my roof.
It's 'cause Hana
gave him jalapeño dip.
It's not that hot.
Well, you don't eat
the whole container, dear.
Never in a million years
did I think that Gao
would bring a Buddymonster
home with him one day.
I couldn't agree more.
It's surprising enough
that you got a Buddymonster,
but beating Tasuku Ryuenji
in a Buddyfight?
Wait till the guys at
the club hear about that one.
I was there and
watched the whole match.
It was the coolest
thing I've ever seen!
He did his Mighty
Sun Fighter speech and...
Uh, she's just kidding.
What's this called?
It's my homemade pudding.
Try it, you might like it.
Hmm.
(sniffs)
Oh, yeah!
It's amazing!
Oh, good, then I'll
have a fresh batch ready
by the time you get
home from school today.
Sweet!
‐Gotta run!
‐'Kay, bye!
See you later, dear.
Hope you have
a wonderful day.
♪
Study hard, guys.
‐We will, Daddy.
♪
Where are all the
other monsters today?
Probably at school.
Did you forget
about the special
Buddyfight class
this morning?
Guess all that pudding
melted your brain.
Check it out,
I think that's him.
That's that cool guy
who beat Tasuku Ryuenji.
Looks like you're
famous, big brother.
You know it.
Only to the first graders.
You were majorly lucky,
that's all.
Oh, yeah?
The Mighty Sun Fighter
defeated Tasuku
in that Buddyfight
fair and square!
You're just jealous,
kitten shirt!
It's a tiger!
Anyway, Buddyfight
is just a game of luck.
Pure and simple,
you proved it.
I mean, how else could
a total novice like you
win against a
top class fighter?
Tell me that?
Huh?
♪
Hey, I was talking here!
See you, Hana.
Later.
Why are you
in such a hurry?
I gotta ask Baku a favor.
I want to see if he can
add this card to my deck.
Gargantua Punisher, huh?
Sorry, I can't.
But why not?
Come on, don't
you understand?
Giving me Gargantua Punisher
proves that Tasuku
considers me his rival.
I have to master this card,
no matter what it takes.
Yeah, but only one guy
in the entire world's
been able to use
this card up till now, right?
And frankly, I don't really
know if you've got the skills.
I think this card's a
bit too intense for you.
It would just be
too much right now.
You only got
the thing yesterday,
so what's the big rush?
Deck building
is an art, bro,
and I need time
to work my craft.
Uh?
Statistics show that
adding a card like that
won't necessarily
make your deck better.
What are you
talking about?
This is a super
strong card.
No matter how
strong it is,
if you're not able to
handle it during a battle,
then it's useless to you.
You've really got to know
the exact moment to
cast it from your hand.
It is a special card
and it'd be a bummer
not to use it.
But you're gonna have
to play with it a few times
to get your deck
into game shape.
So then‐‐
You're gonna need a tuner.
What's a tuner?
You seriously don't know?
Okay, now you just
made me all hangry.
Right, don't worry,
I'll explain it.
Well, if he's eating‐‐
Hey, wait, that's my lunch!
A tuner is what we
call a practice partner
who you get along
really well with.
Once I analyze the trial rounds
you have with your tuner,
Baku will rebuild
your deck from there.
That's about
the best way to do it.
Bottom line, bro, no tuner,
no Gargantua Punisher card.
You got me?
I got you.
Have anyone in mind?
Don't sweat it, we've got
the special
Buddyfight class next.
I'm sure I'll find
someone there.
Well, I'll help you
scope out a winner, kid.
Hmm.
(door squeaking)
But the kid needs my help!
Monsters are not allowed in
the classroom during class.
Says who?
Before we begin,
are there any questions
about the strategies
you were asked to memorize
for homework?
Anyone?
Don't be shy now,
take a minute to think.
Bananas?
Gao!
Something you'd like
to share with the class?
I saw some
bananas walk in here.
Bananas?
Tetsuya Kurodake!
What did I tell you about
being late for my class?
Busted.
So tell me, why
are you late this time?
I was dancing, yo.
What?
Like this, yo, yo, yo.
Uh.
Yo, yo, yo, yo‐‐
♪
Everybody, dance with me.
Tetsuya, stop that
foolishness at once,
you hear me!
Come on,
Mr. Neginoyama, you try.
Yo, yo, yo, yo‐‐
♪
(clapping in rhythm)
Woo‐hoo, check
out my sick moves!
♪
I got ants in my pants
and I want to dance!
Awesome!
That guy's incredible!
He's got the teacher hoppin'!
I haven't seen him around.
His name's Tetsuya Kurodake.
He's kind of known
for skipping class.
Do you think he
could be my tuner?
Huh?
I don't know, he's not
much of a fighter, bro.
I agree.
There's just something
about that guy.
Big finish.
Yeah.
(cheering)
I haven't partied
like that since 1999!
Tetsuya!
Huh?
Want to be my tuner?
A tuner, what's that?
All you need to do is have
a few Buddyfights with me.
Hmm, gee, I don't know.
I'd better ask
my buddy about it.
You know what I'm sayin'?
Just chillax here
for a sec, a'ight?
♪
He actually has a buddy?
He says no prob, yo.
But we've got
two conditions.
So, what are they?
First up, you're
gonna have to use a deck
that includes your
Gargantua Punisher.
‐Huh?
What did he say?
And the second one,
if you lose the match
you've got to agree
that you'll never ever use
the Gargantua
Punisher card again.
He can't do that.
Huh, so your buddy drives
a hard bargain, huh?
Yeah, true dat.
Okay.
‐What?
Huh?
But just so we're clear,
if I win...then you've
got to be my tuner, man.
All right, deal.
Huh.
♪
Here we are at Aibo Academy's
fighting stage.
Today we welcome back
a familiar face.
The kid who defeated
Tasuku Ryuenji by pure luck
and who suffers from a major
overconfidence problem,
sixth grader, Gao Mikado.
His challenger,
also a sixth grader,
is Tetsuya Kurodake.
And between you and me,
he's not that good.
But I've got
a feeling even his skills
are more than enough
to take down Gao,
the king of the newbies.
Come on, brother,
you can do it!
I could beat that freak show
with my eyes closed.
(growls)
♪
I added Gargantua Punisher,
but I didn't have time
to even out the deck.
Let's get this
party started, Tetsuya.
Release Baku's
super explosive Dragon Deck,
Dragon Blast Fury, Luminize!
(murmuring)
Time to dance, yo.
Come on, feel the beat,
there's a demon
this time to defeat.
Let's luminize it, yo.
Both fighters have
equipped their core gadgets.
Buddy‐‐
Fight!
‐Let's Raise The Flag.
Dragon World!
Ha ha!
Magic World, you
know what I'm sayin'?
I know you know
what I'm sayin'.
Magic World, huh?
Although the monsters
are somewhat weaker,
their magic is powerful.
♪ Yo, yo, yo, yo, beat me,
you must be dreamin' ♪
♪ 'Cause my posse,
they are demons ♪
♪ They aren't evil
don't get me wrong ♪
♪ Yo, they're legit
and crazy strong ♪
♪ Chicka‐chicka‐chicka ♪
♪ Yo, yo, what ♪
So, where's your buddy?
(chuckles)
He'll be here soon.
(excited murmuring)
It's okay, kids,
don't worry,
there's plenty of
Asmodai to go around.
‐Me next.
‐All right!
You know,
being around all you
makes me feel young again.
(laughing)
And I've been
around a while!
(excited yammering)
Kids, you just
gotta love 'em.
Gao will go first.
Charge and draw.
Ready.
♪
I'm gonna call Extreme Sword
Dragon to the right area.
♪
(growls, grunts)
He looks fierce,
but check this out, yo.
Keep your eyes open,
he'll be using a spell.
I cast Magical Goodbye.
♪
What's that?
♪ Yo, yo, yo,
you look so surprised ♪
♪ I can see it in your eyes ♪
♪ The Magic World's cool ♪
♪ Let me take you to school ♪
♪ I can cast you
in your turn ♪
♪ Talk about a super burn ♪
Hey, hang on a second,
did that move just
force the monster I called
back into my hand somehow?
Wait, it's still
my turn, isn't it?
Huh?
You've got that right.
He hasn't
even attacked yet.
Let's try this again.
I call Extreme Sword
to the right.
Hah!
♪
Ah, what did I do?
Tetsuya wasted his spell!
He returned Gao's
monster to his hand,
but there's no reason Gao
can't just call it again.
Talk about your
total amateur move.
Attack, Extreme!
(roars)
Uh, what the what?
End of move.
(laughing)
I guess you learned from
that mistake, huh, buddy.
Uh?
Hey, that voice!
(gasps)
♪
‐It's Asmodai!
I can't believe it,
the demon Asmodai
who we all know from TV
is actually here
at Aibo Academy!
Question is,
why is he here?
Well, that's 'cause I'm Tetsuya
here's buddy, that's why.
‐What?
Sorry, Asmodai,
I totally messed things up
trying to fight on my own.
My bad, should
have been here
instead of outside
with my fans.
What?
But at least now you know
not to make a mistake
like that again, right?
Everyone messes up sometimes.
The important thing
is to keep trying,
keep getting better,
and to never give up.
Yeah, true dat.
So let's show 'em our stuff.
And win this thing.
Draw.
Charge and draw.
To the right I call
Fallen Angel of Rage, Beleth,
and to the center, Demon
Realm Death Metal, Valefar.
♪
Valefar, attack
Extreme Sword Dragon.
Music is the
heartbeat of battle.
♪
Your rhythm's off!
(explosion)
Now, Beleth, attack Gao.
Your time is up.
I cast and pay one
gauge for Dragon Breath.
I got dressed for this?
End of move.
Gao completely crushed Beleth
with a counter spell card
and escaped this round
with no damage at all!
Hey, did you see that?
Oh, I saw it.
I call to the center
Systemic Dagger Dragon.
To the right,
Thousand Rapier Dragon.
And to the left,
Double Sword Dragon.
Okay, Double Sword Dragon,
go attack Valefar!
Thousand Rapier,
attack Tetsuya!
In vino veritas!
Systemic Dagger,
attack Tetsuya!
I cast Magical Goodbye.
♪
What?
He had another one of
those Magical Goodbye cards?
And this time he knew
exactly when to play it.
Told you you could do it.
Good job, kid.
It's all thanks
to Gao for showing me
how to use a counter spell.
Thank you, Gao.
Your move.
Now it's time for
the real show, yo.
I'm gonna
Buddycall to the center
the one, the only,
Demon Lord, Asmodai.
Am I?
(growls)
Ta‐da!
Tetsuya, you're
the man who's gonna be
the future king
of the Magic World.
Now enchant the people
with that dance of yours
and fight!
♪ Yo, yo, yo, yo ♪
♪ Asmodai's incredible,
you'll see it's so ♪
♪ One second he's there,
but where did he go ♪
♪ Here comes his move,
Dangerous Backdrop, yo ♪
♪
No, Double Sword!
Now I cast Devil Advantage.
♪ I return
Valefar to my hand ♪
♪ Then call his
brother out, too ♪
♪ Send them
right and left ♪
♪ It's a triple
attack, fool ♪
♪ What's this,
oh, no ♪
♪ Asmodai attack
Thousand, yo ♪
Yo, yo, yo!
Yo, yo!
Yo, yo, yo, yo.
(chanting "yo")
Kuguru?
♪ Get 'em on a roll
now I'm in a groove ♪
♪ Time for me to make
my finishing move ♪
Do it, Tatsuya.
On it, A‐dog,
final phase, boy‐ee.
♪
Oh, yeah!
Whoa.
Diabolical Hardcore.
♪
Owned it.
(cheering)
We're done for.
Your move.
Huh, what‐‐your move?
What's wrong with you?
You still have
life points left.
Yeah, you're right!
I hope he
doesn't win this.
It'll prove he was just
lucky the other day.
Buddycall!
Finally, some action!
Drop to the right,
get back a life point
with Buddygift!
I'll equip Steel Fist,
Dragoknuckle.
(shattering)
Oh, no, they're
all coming at once.
Hey, Drum,
attack Asmodai!
(engine roaring)
(laughs gleefully)
Crack, Drill Ram Bunker!
See you on TV, kids!
(explosion)
Take this!
Dragoknuckle!
Tetsuya has only
four life points left!
And by inflicting that
damage with Dragoknuckle,
Gao adds plus one
to his gauge.
With a gauge
of four and his opponent
with four life
points or less‐‐
And don't forget
there are no monsters
in the center areas.
Final phase cast!
♪
Airpax!
Gargantua Punisher!
That's pretty big, yo!
♪
Game over,
winner is Gao Mikado.
Huh, I'm kicking butt
and taking names.
(cheering)
You see that,
my brother won again!
Uh, I could have
done it in less time.
That's right,
Gargantua Punisher,
the amazing card
that only one person
in this world can use.
And for right now, that
card belongs to Gao Mikado.
You got me, yo.
Hey, if you're
still up for it,
I don't mind
being your tuner.
Thanks, but I don't really
care about that anymore.
Huh?
I'd much rather
you be my friend.
I think you're
totally awesome!
Really?
(laughing)
I'm sure that this defeat
will make you stronger.
Feel free to fight
with my buddy anytime, Gao.
I'd like that,
what do you think?
Cool, but next time
you're mine, yo.
Well, what do you know?
I guess a guy like that
could be a tuner after all.
Excuse me, Asmodai?
Why did you include
Gargantua Punisher
as a condition to fight?
Hey, isn't it obvious?
To add some excitement
to the fight, yo.
Huh?
'Cause let's be honest,
I do know a thing or two
about entertaining
the people of Earth.
(laughing)
(door opening)
What are you doing in here?
Just thinking about
today's Buddyfight.
Yeah?
To make the most out
of Gargantua Punisher,
I should reconstruct my deck.
Thing is, I don't
have enough monsters.
I could add some
dragon knights.
Dragon knights?!
I can't believe
you'd do that to me!
I don't want to fight
with guys like that!
Hey, no need to flip out.
Um, what exactly are
you eating there, kid?
Pudding‐‐Mom left some in
our room with a note by it.
Let's see.
Here‐‐Gao, I made
this pudding for Drum,
so don't eat it under
any circumstances.
Oops, sorry,
I guess it was...
yours.
You're no longer my buddy!
♪
Hello there, I'm Paruko,
here to guide you
through the world
of Buddyfight.
Buddyfight cards
are classified
according to the world
where the monsters live.
But you knew that.
So, before
you build a deck,
you need to chose the world
that you want the cards from.
For example, Tasuku
Ryuenji and Gao Mikado
picked the Dragon World.
But Tetsuya Kurodake
uses the Magic World.
There are a few
worlds to choose from,
so do your homework, kids.
Can you open a
buddy rare card?
What do you think?
♪
So you want to learn
to Buddyfight, do you?
Well, then I'll
teach you everything
you need to know, kid.
Huh, what do you mean
the Castle Store manager's
gonna teach you?
Fine, whatever.
Next time, The Rules
of Buddyfight!
Join us for a Buddyfight.