Do you have what it
takes to Buddyfight?
Choose your favorite world
and use special cards
to summon its powerful
monsters into reality.
Challenge other fighters and
Buddy Call your toughest ally
to fight by your side.
Get ready to raise the flag.
♪
No way!
Use that card to help me evolve.
Huh, I'm way ahead of you, man.
I pay one gauge and evolve!
I knew you had it in you!
Let's see your true form!
Super Armordragon,
Drum Breaker Dragon
is on the scene!
I never doubted you
for a second, my son.
Spinning Blasting
Assault, Mobile Ram,
Drill Ram Breaker!
(grunting)
♪
I've never been so proud, not
since he first breathed fire.
Don't forget about
my Penetrate ability.
Here's my
Dragon Sword, Drumsword.
♪
Game over.
Winner: Gao Mikado.
Yeah!
Dad taught me everything I know.
Today's training is over.
You did well to find
him for your buddy.
♪
(yawning)
(crickets chirring)
Huh?
♪
You okay, Z?
Hey, why are you still up?
Tasuku's autograph?
I didn't know you were
still holding onto that thing.
So, what if I am?
It happens to mean a lot to me.
It's all right,
you're not the only one.
I'm worried about him, too.
It feels like he's
been missing for ages.
I'm sure he'll be okay.
He's as tough as they come.
It's just that...
That what?
I thought they called
you the Boy Wonder Cop.
If you're not going to
do anything about him,
then I will.
I'll capture the
Grim Reaper myself!
No, it's too dangerous
for you to get involved.
We'll just see about that.
We'll see who's the
real defender of justice.
(sighs)
Mmm.
I want to apologize to him.
I was kind of on edge during
all that Grim Reaper business.
I'm sure you'll get your chance.
Kiri's gone?
Yes.
Where?
I don't know.
He just snuck off one morning.
I'm really sorry.
Huh?
♪
I gotta ask you
for your Buddy Skill.
You can't start
looking for him now.
What about the Gaen Cup?
Relax, we'll be back
way before then.
Where would we start?
He could be anywhere.
‐I think I have a lead.
‐Yeah?
Kiri's an honest guy.
All the buddy monsters he stole
when he was the Grim Reaper,
he's gonna try
and get them back.
‐Gao.
‐Huh?
Guess you didn't hear, huh, bro?
Hear what?
Everyone we know is
posting about it right now.
"All the buddy monsters taken
by the Grim Reaper have..."
"...Have all been returned
to their original owners."
Huh!
♪
What's wrong, did Drum
eat your lunch again?
♪
Well, look who it is.
Should we talk to them?
Hey, Noboru!
What's up?
First I find out that
you're back in town,
then that you're
competing in the Gaen Cup!
Mm‐hm.
What he just said.
Plus I'm still a little confused
how you guys ended up
on the same team.
Is there a secret club
I don't know about?
‐Yeah, is there?
‐What is it?
Well, if you
really want to know,
I'd be happy to tell you.
Spill it, you're
killing us here!
On second thought, maybe not.
What a letdown.
Talk about a buzzkill.
You ill‐mannered mongrel!
Only reason I joined the team
is to return the favor you
did for me in the ABC Cup.
I hope we get to fight then.
Yeah, just make sure that
you win your semifinal match.
Goes without saying that
we'll be winning ours.
He hasn't changed.
I wouldn't be so sure.
I guess we'll look
for you in the finals.
Cool, keep it real, Mikado.
Let's get moving.
Come on, Kitten Shirt.
What do I keep telling you?
It's a tiger!
'Kay, catch ya later, man.
We're gonna lay low.
We're meeting Tetsuya
and Zanya in a few.
Break a leg out there!
You, too; later.
So, tell me, Kitten Shirt.
It's a tiger!
Sorry, I couldn't resist.
But I heard what
you said to Gao.
Whatever, it was just talk.
I get it, okay, we're doing this
to help Gao and be his backup.
‐Yeah.
‐Just as long as you remember
that our goal here is
not to win this thing.
(grumbling)
Welcome back to our
Gaen Cup prematch coverage.
It's amazing to think
that the whole world
will be watching today's two
exciting semifinal matches.
Now, over to you, Paruko.
Thanks, Miss Haneda.
Well, as you might expect,
with the first semifinal
match about to begin,
the sold‐out crowd's on
the edge of their seats
here at the Aibo
Academy Fighting Stage,
and with the incredible
matches we've witnessed so far,
who can blame 'em?
The first semifinal of the day
will see Team Purgatory
take on Team Destiny.
Let's make some noise
for the fighters.
And entering the stage now,
Team Destiny's leadoff fighter,
he defeated the
hard‐hitting Seifukai leader,
Genma Todoroki,
in the first round,
all the way from
America, Noboru Kodo!
And he'll be facing
another majorly tough fighter
from Team Purgatory.
Everyone give it up
for the one, the only,
Rouga Araga‐‐huh?
♪
‐Huh?
I've never seen a player
in an outfit like that.
Is he trying to
intimidate his opponent,
or does he just
like to wear armor?
Either way, he's an
imposing presence,
but without seeing his
face, that's all I got.
Uh...
Attention, please.
His name is Purgatory Knight.
And the armor that he's wearing
is actually a Core Gadget.
Well, there you have it, folks.
And as far as I can tell,
he's not officially
breaking any rules.
That Core Gadget's
really tough looking.
Core Gadgets are
just reflections
of the fighter's
inner hopes and dreams.
The Core Deck Case
can change itself
into a symbol that gives
the fighter strength
or make itself match with
what a fighter really wants
on the inside.
Your cool spear is kind
of a perfect example.
It represents both your
straightforward determination
to fulfill your dreams and
your idolization of knights.
So his Core Gadget
turned into a suit of armor
to hide his true identity.
That's it, right?
Well, that would be one
assumption that we could make.
Mmm.
Miss Nanana, would you
please begin the fight?
If you'd be so kind.
Kyoya Gaen just said my name!
I think he hearts me.
Oh, no, but I already
have my heart set
on marrying Tasuku Ryuenji.
Uh, did I just
say that out loud?
Both players, please luminize.
(cheering)
With golden wings on my back,
I soar through the sky!
Luminize, Noble Wing Knights!
A binding pact made in shadows.
Gather, all knights of despair!
Dark Luminize,
Purgatory Knights Conviction!
The second round begins now,
so let's Buddy...
Fight!
‐It's time to raise the flag!
I fight for Dragon World.
I'm with Darkness Dragon World.
That makes three users
of Darkness Dragon World.
I wonder if Retsu
built this deck, too.
♪
Noboru will go first.
Charge and draw.
I call Dragon Knight,
Alexander to the center.
An army of sheep led by a lion,
or lions led by a sheep.
I'm countin' on ya, Alexander.
Attack the fighter.
Right!
Gordias Breaker!
♪
End of move.
Just like that, Purgatory
Knight's down three life points.
But he seems to be
totally unfazed by it,
although I guess if he was,
I wouldn't be able to tell.
Just look at that steely glare.
Let's go to work.
Hear that?
He said "go to work."
You know what that means?
But how did‐‐how could
this even be possible?
You wanna explain?
Nin?
♪
I call Purgatory Knights,
Iron Gerd Dragon to the left.
I am the one and only
Iron Gerd Dragon,
leader of the Purgatory
Knights Shock Troopers
and user of the
formidable iron chain.
I Buddy Call
Purgatory Knights Leader,
Demios Sword Dragon.
♪
Feast your eyes on the
strongest of the Armordragons
and hero of national salvation.
Our leader,
Lord Demios Sword Dragon,
has entered the battle.
Wait, did he just
say Armordragon?
Yeah, I don't get it.
As far as I know,
we Armordragons
are Dragon World monsters.
How can a Darkness Dragon
World monster be one of us?
I equip Purgatory Sword, Fatal.
♪
Hey, that sword
looks just like...
Dragon Sword, Dragobrave.
Thanks a lot, Gao.
I'll remember our
fight when I use it.
Wait, isn't that the card
that you gave to Tasuku
as thanks for the
Gargantua Punisher!!?
Mm‐hm.
Weird, Armordragons
and Dragobrave?
They're the same cards
that Tasuku uses.
Is he a fan?
Huh?
I knew it, I knew it was him.
But why, I don't understand.
Of all people, why
would he be doing this?
♪
I set Crush that Body,
and Sustain Mine.
♪
What kind of spell is that?
I've never even
heard of it before.
When that spell's set,
if your monster's destroyed
by another monster's ability,
you can increase your gauge
by one card.
Demios Sword, attack Alexander!
♪
Young knight from
my beloved homeland,
let us do battle.
Yours‐‐it's mine!
♪
Huh?
Demios Retribution!
Iron Gerd, attack the fighter.
It is the ultimate honor for any
warrior to rise to a challenge.
Behold, young knight,
my amazing Iron Gerd!
Ahh!
Demios, activate your ability.
There comes a time
in every battle
where a warrior must
decide what comes first.
Witness the rule of Purgatory.
Great Lord Demios, I humbly
offer you such an honor.
May your victory be sweet.
(groaning)
(screaming)
‐What was that?
‐I think that's
a legendary Purgatory curse.
Purgatory curse?
The rumors say it's this
really dark, secret art
that was once used
in Dragon World.
You see, everyone
thought it was lost,
just like the legendary
Brave Knights who protected
Dragon World from the
Bombers of Darkness.
(groaning)
Demios, attack him again.
Hey, wait!
Demios Retribution!
Ahh!
That Demios Sword
Dragon or whatever,
does it have
a double attack ability?
Uh, well, not exactly, my lady.
So why did he destroy
that Iron Gerd Dragon?
I'm just guessing, but maybe it
lets him attack a second time.
Yes, his ability is triggered
when a teammate
sacrifices himself.
♪
That's one brutal attack.
‐Yeah.
‐I don't believe it.
There's no way that
he'd fight like this!
What's going on with you, Z?
He's onto something.
Here's my Sword of Purgatory!
Purgatory Sword, Fatal
gains one critical point
if your own monster is
destroyed in the field
by the ability of
an opponent's card.
So it's twice as nice with
that Crushing Set Spell.
Now it's payback time.
I cast Green Dragon Shield.
Quick‐thinking Noboru blocks
Purgatory Knight's
vicious attack.
Your move.
Draw, charge and draw.
♪
I Buddy Call Dragon Knight,
El Quixote to the right.
Let's ride.
I call Dragon Knight,
Red Baron to the left.
And I equip.
Soar now, Cavalry
Dragon, Hyperion.
♪
Attack!
I cast Black Dragon Shield.
♪
I'm serious, I know
I heard him say it.
It was the Purgatory Knight.
I'm sure he said,
"Let's go to work."
"Let's go to work"?
What's so weird about that?
Buddy Police officers
always say it
when they're about
to take action.
Huh, the Buddy Police?
Hang on there, bro.
Are you saying what
I think you're saying?
You must've guessed by now.
The cards he's using
are no coincidence.
They're the exact
same ones Tasuku uses.
‐Huh?
‐That's wack, yo.
So the Purgatory Knight's
true identity is Tasuku Ryuenji?
Hmm.
(grunting)
♪
Sword of Purgatory, Fatal!
This guy is really good.
There's no way I'm wrong.
I've seen him fight enough
times to know it's him.
You just blew my mind, yo.
If you're right, then what
do you wanna do about it?
We can't just accuse
him without proof.
Fine, then I'll prove
it to you right now.
Wait, you can't stop the fight!
This oughta be good.
Whatever you do,
I got your back, Z.
Do you think he's right,
is it really Tasuku?
It's hard to be sure,
but if anyone can recognize
their hero, it's Zanya.
Imagine how you'd feel
if someone you idolized
became a member of Disaster.
No wonder our homie's
feeling a little played.
Chill out, man!
Hmm, that's Gao.
Stop, let go of me!
I have to go ask him.
I'll show you I'm right!
‐Come on, big bro.
‐Stop it!
What's going on?
Hey, Gao, keep
your dog on a leash.
Zanya from Team Balle du Soleil
is trying to get
in on the action
while his teammates are trying
to talk some sense into him
and hold him back.
Tell us why you're
dressed like that!
Take off the helmet, Tasuku!
♪
That fool doesn't know what
on Earth he's talking about.
Tasuku Ryuenji had
his Buddy Police status
permanently revoked,
and now he's off doing...
what is that meddlesome
boy up to anyway?
(chuckling)
The nerve!
What a terrible thing
to accuse someone of!
Especially my boyfriend‐‐
I mean, Tasuku Ryuenji.
He's only the idol of all
young Buddyfighters in the world
and the Buddy Police Boy Wonder.
He would never
in a million years
dress up in a suit of armor
to hide his identity.
No chance, no way!
Sorry, Jin.
I know what you said,
but if that is Tasuku,
then I have to beat him.
Stay back, I'm gonna win this!
Huh?
Let's try this again.
I call Alexander
to the left position.
Go, attack Purgatory Knight!
Gordias Breaker!
El Quixote, you're up next.
Ride, Rocinante,
an assault of glory!
I cast Purgatory Flame
that Resides Within the Body.
♪
(shouting)
Cool, another new spell.
By sacrificing one of
his monsters in the field,
Purgatory Knight is
able to neutralize
his opponent's attack.
Uh‐oh, huh?
Technically a counter spell,
it inflicts damage equal to the
sacrificed monster's critical.
♪
(screaming)
Only three life left.
That was such an awesome move.
Whoever this guy is, he rocks!
What happened?
I've followed almost
your whole career,
and you've never been
the type of fighter
who would sacrifice
his own teammates.
Relax, man.
Don't stand there
and try to tell me
you don't feel the same, okay?
Why are you hiding
behind that armor
and not showing your
face to the public?
Actually, let me
answer that for you.
It's because
working for Disaster
is something to be ashamed of!
Same old Zanya.
Once he gets going,
there's no stopping him.
‐Really?
‐Do it quickly.
Of course, you can
count on me, sir.
How could you support
that organization?
Have you forgotten your pride?
You're a Buddy Police officer!
♪
Let's see if this one
jogs his memory a little.
(grunting)
The pride of the Buddy Police.
Here he is at your service.
(gasping)
♪
Zanya was right.
No fair, why couldn't I
be the Purgatory Knight?
Because you're far too lame.
♪
I didn't want to believe it.
Tell me that's a hologram.
Sometimes truth really
is stranger than fiction.
The Purgatory Knight who,
up to now, was just some weirdo
who liked dressing up
in armor is none other
than Tasuku Ryuenji,
the Buddy Police Boy Wonder!
No, my Buddy Police
days are over.
After a while, I realized
how corrupt they'd become.
And the adults who are
running things now,
I never want to be
like any of them.
Huh?
(static flickering)
♪
I can't hear a thing,
what happened?
I guess someone
didn't want us to know
what he was about to say.
I'd have to agree with you.
(crowd murmuring)
♪
I think I get what he meant now.
That weird little guy
who used to be your boss.
You know, your Commander I.
Maybe you could hang
out with him, Noboru,
and try to help
loosen him up a little.
I didn't really understand
why an older kid like you,
you know, who worked
with adults and all,
would want to be friends
with a younger kid like me,
but now I think I do.
Thing is, you need time to
grow up and do kid things.
Being a kid teaches you
a ton about the world
and how we should try to
fit into it as grownups,
but you're not really there yet,
so you shouldn't pretend to be!
And like your
Commander I told me,
you need my help!
(groaning)
How dare you?
How dare you treat
me like a child?
Kids are so powerless,
and I would be, too,
if I didn't change.
You see?
I couldn't even help my family,
so I decided to become an adult.
I went from being protected
to being the protector!
I've never seen him like this.
Don't try and be
something you're not.
Time to put you
out of your misery.
Begin Final Phase, I cast.
Ah, yeah.
It's Noboru's
Combination Impact.
Dragon Knight
Ultimate Technique,
Ultimate Smash!
Counter Final!
I cast.
♪
(clock ticking)
Let the world distort.
Turn back the sands of time and
erase all sadness from the past.
Sword of Nothingness!
Distortion...
Punisher!!
♪
Game over.
Winner: Purgatory Knight.
What?
What happened here,
am I losing it?
It looked like Noboru
was about to clinch it
with his Impact, but then...
somehow the tide
drastically changed.
The Purgatory Knight,
a. k. a. Tasuku Ryuenji,
seems to have deflected
Noboru's Impact
right back at him
to win the game.
♪
It's time for...
Tasuku and Gao's...
Card of the Day!
Today we're gonna talk
about the amazing
Purgatory Knights Leader,
Demios Sword Dragon.
It's a super powerful card
that can do an extra attack
each time you destroy your
own Purgatory Knights monsters.
When you call Demios,
two more Purgatory
Knights monsters,
and equip an item yourself,
you can do up to six
attacks in a row!
How could anyone
compete with that, huh?
So what do you think, guys?
You think you can
open up one of these?
You'll never know until you try!
♪