♪
Do you have what it
takes to Buddyfight?
Choose your favorite world
and use special cards
to summon its powerful
monsters into reality.
Challenge other fighters
and Buddy Call
your toughest ally
to fight by your side.
Get ready to raise the flag!
♪
I guess that means
it's time for final phase!
♪
So this is how
it's gonna end?
I'm disappointed in you, Gao.
Counter final!
I cast!
♪
Let the world distort.
Turn back the sands of time
and erase all
sadness from the past,
Sword of Nothingness,
Distortion Punisher!!
♪
I'll be the one
to save this world.
Even someone like Gao Mikado
won't be able to stand
in the way of my triumph.
♪
Let's give them a hand
for a wonderful fight.
But in the end, there
can only be one champion
and I know who it'll be.
(yelling)
Gao seems to be
preparing an attack.
But aren't his
life points at zero?
Is there anything that
could get him out of this?
I get what you're saying, Baku.
Without life points
and running out of options,
I'm gonna tap into the Dragon
Return System's second ability
which is way more awesome!
Okay, Gao needs to discard
one card off the top of his deck
and hopefully it's a spell card.
♪
It's Green Dragon Shield!
I'm not done.
Our life points will become two.
Say what?!
Gao's still in this?
His Dormant set spell
arose to bring him back to life!
♪
Well, this is new to me.
What's gonna happen next?
His Roaring Slash!!
Gargantua Punisher!!
can't be nullified
and the damage can't be reduced.
♪
Counter spells are useless
against Distortion Punisher!!
so there was no choice,
we had to take the hit
and get back up
at our first chance.
Endurance pays off.
It's not over yet, cousin.
You'll see.
(soft rumbling)
I activate Crush that Body,
and Sustain Mine's ability.
♪
You're kidding me,
I didn't know his spell
had a second ability as well.
When my life points
would become zero,
I can choose to
destroy this card
to discard the top
card from my deck.
And if it happens
to be a spell, then...
It's a Black Dragon Shield!
I know what that means.
My life points become two.
I've never seen
a Buddyfight keep going
after two impact
cards were used.
No matter who wins,
this game is legendary.
It's one epic
battle here today.
Both players were hit
by impact cards
but have managed
to come out of it
with two life points each!
No one forgets
a match like this!
‐We should be there!
‐Hm.
You're right, we
shouldn't wait any longer.
♪
Tasuku just pulled
Distortion Punisher!! again.
That won't be any
use to him now.
♪
He sent it to his gauge.
From here on out, this is
gonna be a no guard battle.
It looks that way.
Get 'em, Gao!
(grunts)
You want us to
suspend the Gaen Cup?
It is out of the question
to do this so late in the match!
We need to question
Kyoya Gaen right away
and then we have
to stop his plans.
I wish there was
something we could try
but as you say,
our hands are tied.
You have to believe him!
‐Huh?
‐I saw the danger myself!
(rumbling, exclaiming)
What on earth is that?!
♪
It's the portal that
connects directly
to Darkness Dragon World!
I don't understand,
who sanctioned this portal?
That's just it,
no one did!
They're planning
to invade the earth.
He speaks the truth!
I saw it with my own eyes.
The monsters of
Darkness Dragon World
were gathering and
getting ready to attack.
♪
What was that?
(exclaiming)
(murmur of crowd exclamations)
♪
(gasps)
(crowd screaming)
♪
Hey, I think that's a monster
from Darkness Dragon World!
How could this happen?
Kazane, calm down, dear.
Where have you been?
I've got your back, my boy.
‐Huh?
‐It's about to get nasty.
Tasuku, did you know about this?
But they weren't supposed
to get here so soon.
(exclaims)
No matter.
♪
I will still defeat them.
Disaster Force activate!
♪
Time to go to work!
You were undercover?
Dark Buddy Skill on.
Purgatory Sword, Fatal!
(dragon shrieking)
(yells)
No, Tasuku!
Hm.
We made a few modifications
to your Dark Core.
We made it so you can't
even leave a scratch
on Darkness Dragon
World monsters.
I'm powerless.
I should have known.
How can this be?
Dear boy, you really
didn't suspect a thing?
You honestly thought
we'd be foolish enough
to trust a former
Buddy Cop like you?
Oops, I mean, uh, shh,
surprise, we were on to you
from the beginning.
This is unforgiveable;
You hear me?
It's never okay
to rig a Buddyfight.
How dare you betray
my friend like that?
Future Force on.
Hey, what's happening?
What, he's got the
same ability as Tasuku?
Mm‐hm.
Huh, how long have you been
standing behind me, yo?
Gao has the Future Force?
It was just a matter of time
before he realized
his potential.
♪
Since ancient times,
a leader rises when he's needed.
Now he's really
the Mighty Sun Fighter!
♪
Now I cast!
Buddy Skill on.
Dragoenergy!
♪
(groans)
What did we just witness?
Does Gao possess the
same incredible power
the members of
Team Purgatory have?
It's like something
out of a movie
or a really crazy dream.
‐This is no dream.
‐Huh, who said that?
I did, Commander I
of the Buddy Police.
(crowd exclaiming)
What is he doing here?
Please listen to me.
The earth is being invaded
by thousands of
dangerous monsters
from Darkness Dragon World.
You mean this isn't
just part of the game?
They're trying
to open a portal
linking their world to ours
so that all of them
can get through at once.
If we don't act fast,
they could take over
our entire planet.
As for you, Mr. Gaen,
we know that you're
involved in this somehow.
You have been
greatly misinformed.
We found Elf Kabala's
research facility.
You ordered him
to build it, didn't you?
To gain access to other worlds.
Are you gonna deny it?
‐You've got it all wrong.
‐Huh?
You're right about Kyoya Gaen
and the rest of
us Disaster members.
We've known about
their plan for some time
but that's the reason
we've all been learning
to perfect our use
of Disaster Force.
To protect earth from
these devastating monsters
and send them back
where they came from!
Why didn't he tell us?
I guess the secret's out.
I'll tell you everything
you wanna know.
It began with my company's
applied sciences division.
While researching Buddy cards,
we stumbled upon
the existence
of Darkness Dragon World,
which until then was no
more than an urban legend.
We uncovered their plot
to invade earth.
At first, we just trapped
them in Buddy cards
but we knew this
wouldn't work forever.
The only way to defeat them
would be to harness the power
that the Dark Core unleashes,
the Disaster Force.
We've been training
those gifted fighters
who are able to use it.
But why didn't you report this
discovery to the Buddy Police?
I'll tell you why!
Because you adults have shown
that you cannot be trusted!
Hm?
That can't be true.
It was four years ago,
after that terrible day,
when I decided that things
needed to change.
I knew I had to grow up
and become an adult
so that I could
help other kids.
If that's true,
then why did you become
a member of Disaster?
You know why!
You let the Buddy Police
fall to Nobari.
After that,
the only option I had
was to join Kyoya.
I wanted to see justice done
and battling alongside him was
the only way that could happen!
Hm.
We need some of you
out there to join us.
Finding young hopefuls
was my reason
for hosting this tournament.
Those of you born
with the natural talent
to wield the exquisite
powers of the Disaster Force.
We desperately
need your skills.
You kids are the future.
I believe in you.
Use your Dark Core
to save the earth.
(cheering)
(chanting "Kyoya")
♪
Hm, so, what do we do now?
We can't arrest him, can we?
Thanks to Nobari,
the Buddy Police
has a bad enough
PR problem as it is.
He's won them over
with one little speech,
they're treating
him like a king.
I guess we'll have to wait
and see how this plays out.
(growling)
Kyoya, Kyoya,
Kyoya, Kyoya, Kyoya!
You're right, that kind
of power is pretty awesome,
but we're not quite done yet.
What do ya say, huh?
You mind if we
continue our fight now?
Huh, let me see.
‐Is that okay?
‐Oh, it's more than okay.
I want the whole world
to know about the power
of the Dark Core Deck Case.
You heard the guy,
it's your move.
Come on, Tasuku, bring it.
Huh; Right.
I cast Abyss Symphony.
That spell card lets
Tasuku draw two cards.
He can only play 'cause
his life is below six.
I call to the left
Purgatory Knights,
Sword Breaker Dragon.
Attack the fighter!
Say goodbye to that sword
you're so proud of!
What do ya mean?
Dragobreaker!
(grunting)
(groaning)
Why can't you see that
what you're doing is wrong?
I thought you would
understand by now.
I'm doing all of this
to save the world.
Then why go it alone?
Why not come and ask me
or someone else for help?
Like you would have before!
♪
Because the monsters
of Darkness Dragon World
aren't easy to deal with.
In order to fight them,
you have to detach
from your true Buddy monster
and pair up with a Buddy
you have no ties to.
♪
You and Drum are best friends.
I wanted you two to continue
having fun Buddyfights
and I didn't want you
to have to risk everything
like I did.
You should hold on to
this phase of your life
for as long as you can.
Yeah, well, I still think
you're making a huge mistake!
♪
I'm just trying to help.
What are you trying to
grow up so fast for anyway?
Shouldn't we all
be fighting together
and growing up as friends
like we're supposed to?
I'm asking you!
I guess I was
kidding myself
when I thought you'd understand
my intentions are good.
This is the final blow!
No, I cast
Dragonic Formation.
Huh?
Forgive me for this one, Dagger.
Don't worry about it.
End of move.
Your move.
Maybe this'll convince you.
Draw!
Charge and draw.
It's that last card you put in.
I call Jackknife Dragon
to the center!
I thought you might
try something like that.
All right, Jack,
go show the fighter
how strong you are!
Could this game
have any more drama?
Tasuku's ex‐Buddy monster
is gonna be fighting
against him!
Tasuku, you're only
fooling yourself.
Say what you mean!
I know why you became
a member of Disaster.
At first it was the only way
to make sure justice was served.
But be honest, you've
begun to have doubts.
That's not true!
You started wondering
if you'd made a mistake,
if Kyoya and the others could
truly help you with your cause.
You questioned if you were
where you were supposed to be.
But you were afraid,
afraid of admitting
you'd made a mistake!
You're wrong!
My sense of justice
has never led me astray!
♪
You're unable to admit
when you're wrong.
That proves you're
still a child.
So now, give up this
charade and leave Disaster.
Jackknife Battle Blade!
No, Jack, I cast
Black Dragon Shield!
End of move.
Your move.
I've survived harder
moments than this.
I'm not about to give up.
I have a duty to
protect everyone.
I call Demios Sword Dragon
to the right!
♪
What seems to be wrong?
Why are you so worked up?
Just do what I say.
Now, Demios, Sword Breaker,
do a Link Attack
and silence Jackknife Dragon
and show him the
error of his ways!
Now I cast
Dragon Barrier!
♪
Huh?
Not a problem.
I activate Demios' ability.
Kanonas Katharterio!
(yelling)
♪
Don't you get it?
The reason Purgatory
Knight accepted me
as his Buddy is simple.
You don't have the guts
to do what's necessary to win.
You have no idea
what a true challenge is.
Huh?
I'll never let someone like you
take Tasuku away from me!
What are you
waiting for, Demios?
Hurry!
Attack Jack at once!
Oh wow, this is getting serious.
At least you'll lose with
honor to a real‐life hero.
And I cast Dragoenergy!
Huh?
(yelling)
There it is,
Dragoenergy adds 3,000
to the Power and Defense
of an Armordragon
and gives him a counterattack.
Talk about a costly mistake.
Tasuku must have forgotten
than Gao had a Dragoenergy
in his hand when he sent that
Darkness Dragon World monster
back through the
hole in the sky.
I wouldn't wanna
be him right now.
(grunts)
Blade Terminate!
♪
You'll see, Jackknife,
as long as you obsess
over my Buddy,
you'll know what
it means to be lost!
♪
I'll agree to disagree.
End of move.
Huh, Purgatory Knight's
center is wide open.
And see that?
Just three life points.
With no cards left in his hand,
I'd say this is over.
You really think I haven't
prepared for every possibility?
♪
The judges have found
that Gao Mikado's use
of Jackknife Dragon is illegal.
I've been asked to remove
the monster from play.
I cast.
‐Huh?
‐Berserk Gard.
♪
Tasuku!
(grunting)
What's wrong with you?
Stop interfering!
♪
Please, Tasuku.
You keep saying you want to
save the entire world, right?
But tell me,
who's gonna save you?
♪
That's it, you can do it.
The Star Pulsar?
Time to release
the Future Force!
♪
(shrieks)
Hm, the Future Force, you say?
I'll admit that look suits
you a whole lot better.
(panting)
How did this happen?
He destroyed the Dark Core
that I gave him myself.
Um, just wondering, do you
think it would be okay
if they kept Buddyfighting now?
Yeah, of course,
I'd never want to stop
a super‐awesome match
like this, man!
Then it's Gao's move.
Draw.
Charge and draw!
Jackknife, unfold first mode.
Become one with
the lightning
and strike him down
with your power!
Prevail Jackknife
"Thunder Storm"!
♪
Get ready!
Tasuku!
I'm sorry, Jack.
♪
Game over,
winner, Gao Mikado.
♪
Yes!
I owe it all to my team.
(cheering)
There you have it.
Team Balle du Soleil
has won the Gaen Cup!
‐We did it!
‐What an incredible finish!
(cheering)
Is Tasuku gonna be all right?
It's one of the
consequences of wearing armor
made out of the Dark Core.
He just needs to rest a while.
Well, Mr. Mikado,
congratulations.
‐Huh?
‐As a reward
for winning my tournament,
I'd like to offer you
the gift of friendship.
That thing has nothing
to do with friendship!
Is that so?
Allow me to let you in
on a little secret.
The power that opens the gate
to Darkness Dragon World
is actually my Disaster Force.
What did you say?
I believe that the
problems of this world
are too great to resolve.
The only solution is to take
control of the adult world
so we can rebuild
things from scratch.
♪
That's why we're
going to summon
all of those Dark Dragons
through the portal.
That won't help!
It's also why we're
trying to find as many
skilled Disaster Force
users as we can.
You saw how the portal
started to open.
That was just the beginning.
♪
Selected children
from all over the world
will tap into their
Disaster Force potential
and together we'll help
form a giant gateway.
Listen to yourselves.
You can't really be serious.
We'll tell everyone
everything you just told us!
Do what you think is best.
You don't care?
You forget, everyone thinks
that young Master Kyoya
is the hero of the hour.
Do you really think
they're going to believe
what you say?
Then maybe I'll just have to
beat you in a Buddyfight!
It won't take long
for people to see you
for what you really are.
Uh, sorry to interrupt,
but we're coming back live
from our commercial break,
so do you think it would
be all right if I interviewed
the winner now?
I've got something better.
Attention,
now hear this!
Great news, I have just
been challenged to a Buddyfight
by Gao Mikado!
And, of course,
I intend to accept.
Are you sure about that, Gao?
Challenging our hero,
Kyoya Gaen, to a Buddyfight?
I know you've
never lost a fight,
but think about
what you're doing.
Making an enemy of Kyoya Gaen
is not the best choice.
I mean, it's like making
the whole world your enemy.
Well, this oughta be good.
Looks like Gao's
in over his head.
I'll take care of all
the arrangements personally.
I'm looking forward to it, Gao.
Everything that happens
is as Master Kyoya wishes.
Going against him is
like going against nature.
Whatever, even if
the whole world
is against us like you say,
I'll fight alongside
this kid to the very end
because we have a bond that
you could never understand!
We're Buddies!
‐It's time for...
‐Tasuku and Gao's...
‐Card of the day!
Today we're gonna talk to you
about the really cool set spell,
Dragon Return System.
Yeah, it's a good card to have.
When one of your monsters
returns to your deck,
your gauge is boosted by one!
In the event your life
points would become zero,
you can discard the
top card of your deck
to your drop zone
and if that top card's
a spell card...
You're back in the game
'cause your life points
would become two!
So what do ya think, guys?
You think you can
open up one of these?
You'll never know
until you try!
♪
Next time, Gao squares
off with Kyoya Gaen
and while the Dark Core replicas
start to wreak havoc,
Tasuku pays Gao a visit
and you won't believe
what he tells him!
Next episode:
Join us for a Buddyfight!