Do you have what it
takes to Buddyfight?
Choose your favorite world
and use special cards
to summon its powerful
monsters into reality.
Challenge other
fighters and Buddy Call
your toughest ally
to fight by your side.
Get ready to raise the flag!
Reveal Jackknife Thunder Storm!
♪
Get ready!
‐Tasuku!
‐I'm sorry, Jack.
♪
Game over.
Winner: Gao Mikado.
♪
It's no surprise that
Team Balle du Soleil
is the hot topic of the week.
As winners of the Gaen Cup,
these Aibo Academy fighters
will go down in history.
Congratulations to Gao Mikado,
Zanya Kisaragi,
and Tetsuya Kurodake.
Of course, Mr. Gaen,
the sponsor of the Cup,
stole the show with a
shocking announcement.
I wanted all of you to
hear this from me first.
I have great news, I have
just been challenged
to a Buddyfight by Gao Mikado,
and of course,
I intend to accept.
Though there's no record
of him participating
in any official Buddyfights,
it's no secret that Kyoya Gaen
is widely regarded as one of
the world's most elite players.
We now take you to
our voice on the street.
Who will you be cheering for
in the big fight, Kyoya or Gao?
Kyoya without a doubt, the
match will be over in seconds.
Yeah, after all he's
done to protect us
from the Darkness
Dragon World invasion
I'm sure he can
handle Gao Mikado.
How can you even compare
Kyoya to that kid, I mean‐‐
He's the dreamiest
guy on the planet!
There you have it,
the results of our voice
on the street poll are in.
Statistics indicate overwhelming
support for the dreamy hero,
and sadly, not one single vote
in support of the Sun Fighter.
They don't know what
they're talking about!
‐My brother's gonna win!
‐Yeah!
‐Gao's gonna totally shred it!
‐He has to if we're gonna stop
all those Darkness
Dragon World monsters.
Right, but unfortunately,
there's no sure thing when
it comes to a Buddyfight.
♪
I believe that the
problems of the this world
are too great to resolve.
The only solution is to take
control of the adult world
so we can rebuild
things from scratch.
That's why we're
going to summon all
of those Dark Dragons
through the portal.
I wanted to do something
special for you guys
to celebrate winning
the Gaen Cup.
So let's get this party going!
Couldn't have said
it better, Dad.
Come on, let's dig in, guys!
(indistinct conversations)
(birds chirping)
(snoring)
(door opening)
You're up early.
Hey, didn't mean
to wake you, man.
I just had a weird dream.
Why are you up so early, kid?
I need to go see Tasuku.
(background chatter)
I wish you'd called first.
Tasuku isn't receiving
visitors at the moment.
Oh, okay.
What now, breakfast?
Can you give him something?
I suppose, what is it, Gao?
Yeah, is it food, are
you holding out on me?
Just something I think
he should have back.
But are you sure?
(knocking)
Tasuku, it's me.
Can I come in?
I already told
you guys everything
I know about Disaster.
I wish I could be more help.
(footsteps approaching)
Gao left this for you.
What's the matter?
I can't accept it, no way.
I don't have the right
to own that card.
None of that matters.
Don't forget, we're family.
Jack?
Long time.
Why are you so‐‐
I can't show up in my usual
form at a hospital, now can I?
(grunting)
(laughing)
♪
I'll have to thank Gao
when I get out of here.
Yeah, he's a thoughtful
one, that kid.
He knows that what you
need the most right now
is a familiar face.
I really let everybody
down, I messed up.
Didn't I?
There's no going back.
I can't be your Buddy again.
I remember when you became
the Purgatory Knight.
You know what you told me?
The truth is, as long
as I'm protected by you,
I can't become stronger,
I hope you understand.
Even though you're
my best friend,
‐you're my greatest weakness.
‐What're you saying?
♪
Question is, did you
really mean that?
♪
Am I your greatest weakness?
I know you had your reasons for
choosing Demios Sword Dragon
over me, but he didn't
lead you to victory.
Do you think you made
the right decision?
♪
I don't know if it was
a good move or not.
‐But‐‐
‐What is it?
I've made enough mistakes.
I've told myself
no more regrets!
It's okay.
We can't be right
about everything.
I couldn't change things
even if I wanted to.
There's something
you don't know.
Forgive me, I dissolved
our Buddy Contract.
How, I never agreed to that?
You're not grown up yet, Tasuku.
Don't be so hard on yourself.
All of us, even dragons, take
the wrong path sometimes.
It's never too late
to find yourself again.
‐I don't know, Jack.
‐I once told you
you can start over again
as many times as you need.
‐Really, is that true?
‐The most important thing
is to have the courage
to admit your mistakes.
True fighters never run
away from their problems,
even when things get tough.
Then I, I, uh‐‐
okay, I admit that I made
a terrible mistake!
I should've never
pushed you away!
That's better, so, is there
anything you wanna say to me?
♪
I'm sorry.
I'm so sorry, Jack.
(crying)
I forgave you a long
time ago, Tasuku.
We're Buddies till the end.
Right, we're in this together.
Thank you, Jack.
♪
Do you think Tasuku and Jack
will go back to being Buddies?
I don't know, I guess
that'll be up to them.
‐Gao!
‐Huh?
Hey guys, what's wrong?
You won't believe it,
we have to do something!
Chillax, dudes, there's
enough for everyone!
(indistinct remarks)
‐All right, who's next?
‐Wicked!
Tell all your friends
where you got it.
Castle's the coolest place to
get all your Buddyfight stuff.
Dark Core Deck Cases?
♪
‐This is our busiest day ever.
‐Should we get one?
If you don't soon
they're gonna run out.
‐Huh?
‐Come on, get with the times.
We already got ours.
Here, thanks for waiting.
Are they in a trance?
The Dark Core Deck Case
replicas that were handed out
on a trial basis during
the Gaen Cup final round
are now officially
being distributed.
As you can imagine, children
everywhere are lining up
outside local shops to try them.
Joining us now is the
popular young leader
of the Gaen Financial Group,
the company
distributing these cases.
Some are hailing him
as a world‐class hero.
Today, we get a chance to catch
up with the man of the hour.
Thank you for being here.
It's my pleasure.
I, uh‐‐well, let's get started.
Could you tell our viewers
why you're handing out
the Dark Core Deck Cases?
Of course, it's part of
our plan to save the world
from the impending invasion
from Darkness Dragon World.
Oh, I see, but I don't
understand how the distribution
of the cases could lead to
the survival of our world.
Well, if we're forced to
fight against the monsters
of Darkness Dragon World,
we're going to need
all hands on deck,
especially the kids.
They're the only
ones who can control
the phenomenal power
of Disaster Force.
You'll remember
we first witnessed
Disaster Force at the Gaen Cup.
Team Purgatory's Rouga
Aragami was the first
to demonstrate this
incredible ability.
Followed by his teammate,
Sofia Sakharov,
they surprised everyone
when they made
the power of their cards real.
Yes, the Dark Core Deck
Case is the only way
someone can tap into
this unstoppable power.
But Disaster?
Many of our viewers
have concerns about
the sense of doom
the name conveys.
We're committed to preventing
all kinds of disasters.
That's why we gave it that name.
I chose it myself.
I've got a few names for him.
Tell me you're not
cool with this.
‐Cool with what?
‐Doesn't it bother you
how many lies are coming
out of this guy's mouth?
Sure, but what he says won't
matter when we win the fight
and show everyone that he's
not who they think he is.
Agh, I can't wait
to beat this guy!
You said it, let's go.
Where to now?
We got some work to do.
Let's kick Explosive
Dragon Fang up a notch.
Are you really gonna
go through with it, bro?
Fighting Kyoya Gaen
is a huge deal.
If you ask me, I think
it's a big mistake.
Really, Z?
‐Not you too?
‐What's your beef?
Why ya cramping his style, yo?
‐Isn't it obvious?
‐I miss a lot of stuff.
Ever since his publicity
stunt on network TV,
Kyoya's gotten a fresh
rep as Earth's big hero,
and by fighting against him,
those who don't know Gao
will see him as some bad guy.
But that's not really fair.
I mean, it's not like
Gao's done anything wrong.
I can't believe the whole
world's been conned
by Kyoya Gaen's power and
charisma, it turns my stomach.
What's worse is that he's giving
away those Dark Core Deck Case
replicas hoping to find new
unsuspecting Disaster members.
I totally feel your pain, yo!
If people think they can grab
some of that awesome power,
then almost anyone
will support Kyoya!
I hate to break it to you, Gao,
but with the number of fans
you have, you might as well
be from another planet.
♪
(indistinct conversations)
Just ignore them, kid.
They'll all be learning
the truth soon enough.
‐Hey, it's Gao Mikado!
‐Huh?
I don't want you going near
him, he's not a nice boy.
Hey, nobody talks about
my Buddy like that!
‐Relax, it's fine.
‐But, kid‐‐
You said it yourself, pretty
soon they'll all know the truth.
We gotta make sure
we win our fight.
‐Now let's go practice.
‐Okay.
♪
If you're good maybe we can
stop for a snack on the way.
♪
(shouting)
That's it, Gao, you're
gonna own this guy!
Hana, we don't
wanna distract him.
Oh.
He needs to focus.
♪
Everything that happens
is as Master Kyoya wishes.
Going against him is
like going against nature.
(grunting)
(yelling)
(thudding)
(phone ringing)
Hello?
Gao, is that you?
Uh, hi, Mom.
‐How are you doing?
‐Okay, I guess.
I know Dad told
you what's going on,
and I don't know
why I called, but‐‐
It's all right, dear,
I can understand
what you must be going
through right now.
Yeah.
Don't worry, all right?
Even if it seems like the
whole world is against you,
I'll always be on your
side supporting you.
Now then, go train hard
and win your fight.
I believe in you.
You are the Mighty Sun
Fighter after all.
(snoring)
I wish there was something
I could do to help him.
I am his Buddy, after all.
Huh?
(knocking)
Tasuku, what's up?
Hey, I didn't mean
to bother you, but,
after all that's happened,
I was hoping we could talk.
Hey, Mini Jack,
you got a new look!
It's easier to go
through doors like this.
It makes you look
tough, kind of.
(laughing)
So, what's up?
‐I just wanted to say thank you.
‐What?
I've been meaning to
come and see you sooner,
but to be honest, I've
been too embarrassed
about everything that went down.
Don't sweat it,
no need to thank me.
You know, you are like the Sun.
Your kindness and support
helped to shed light
on the darkness that I felt.
My fear of helplessness
made me weak.
So I gave in to Kyoya
and his dark power.
I became lost and made a
decision that I now regret.
I closed myself off to
everyone who cared about me.
♪
I don't want any
friends or family.
I wanna be all on my own.
But you and Jack
never gave up on me.
You kept pushing me
and challenging me.
I'll never forget it.
Now, I know you have
this big fight coming up.
‐Are you okay?
‐I don't know.
There's so much riding
on the outcome.
The entire future of the
world is all up to me.
It's a lot of pressure
to be under.
It's not just that Kyoya's
an awesome Buddyfighter.
I mean, he beat you so he
must be really skilled.
It's the fact that everyone
thinks he's some kinda hero.
People actually think
he's trying to help them.
Like he'll protect them from
the Darkness Dragon World.
What a joke!
I wish there was some way
I'd be guaranteed not to lose.
Gao!
That's enough of
that talk, ya hear?
Don't forget half the
battle of winning a match
like this is staying positive.
Come on, kid, what you need
to be thinking about now
isn't a way not to lose, but
a way you can win the fight!
You taught me that, remember?
When we first became buddies!
It was your confidence
and courage that made me
wanna be your Buddy
in the first place.
Come on, what's the matter?
Easy, Drum, what we should
be thinking about now
is not how to avoid losing,
but how we're gonna win.
Draw!
Time to charge, eh?
Just 'cause you used Dragobrave
doesn't guarantee you the win!
Tasuku's only holding
size two monsters
and offensive spell
cards in his hand.
And how do you know that?
If he doesn't, then there's
no chance I can win.
The only way I'm gonna
defeat him is for me
to believe in myself
and make the draw!
Okay, here goes nothing.
(shouting)
♪
Dragonblade!
Dragobrave!
♪
No way, he drew it!
All right, Drum, you go first.
Okay!
(engine roaring)
Crash!
Drill Ram Bunker!
♪
Is that ringing any bells?
Thanks for reminding me.
I owe you one, Drum.
That's not necessary,
it's what Buddies are for.
But if you wanna give me
your pudding for a week‐‐
All right, you got it.
Okay, that's enough.
Oh, sorry.
(laughing)
Don't let all this
warm and fuzzy stuff
distract you from
our preparation.
Huh, what do you mean?
Isn't there something
you wanna ask him?
♪
Oh yeah, I totally forgot.
Tasuku, you know Kyoya's deck
pretty well, don't you?
I guess, I only fought him once.
So it's not like I know
all his cards or anything,
but I'm happy to tell you
everything I do know.
I think together we could
beat Kyoya once and for all.
You're laughing?
I just think this
is gonna be fun.
What did you say?
You do realize how important
this fight is, don't you, kid?
You know the whole
world is relying on you
to save them by
beating this guy.
All those people out there
who think Disaster's good
need to be brought
back to reality.
How do you call that fun?
‐Uh, uh‐‐
‐Drum has a point,
‐for once.
‐Yeah.
I don't believe you guys!
This is no time to
be joking around.
I don't get how the
three of you can stay
so relaxed at a time like this.
‐It's all 'cause of you, Buddy.
‐Huh?
Before you reminded me, I
forgot about being positive
and focusing all my energy
on winning instead of losing.
I'm lucky to have
you for a Buddy.
The thing is you've done a lot
more for me than you know.
You helped me fight and
make friends with Tasuku.
And 'cause of you,
I have the confidence
to know we're gonna beat Kyoya.
That's why I can
relax and have fun.
Let's make it the
best match ever!
Well, since you
put it like that,
‐let's show this guy who's boss.
‐Okay!
Now, let's talk about
all of that pudding.
I knew it.
He is like the Sun.
‐Tasuku.
‐Huh?
What're you doing here?
I need you to lend
me your power.
Why?
Please, it's the only
way to stop Kyoya Gaen.
♪
Everything is preceding right
on schedule, Master Kyoya.
We're just waiting for
you to give the order.
The world will look
a lot different
when we're done with it.
Da.
Now, finally, I can hide
the Sun in total darkness.
‐It's time for‐‐
‐Tasuku and Gao's‐‐
‐Card of the Day!
Today we're excited to tell you
all about the strongest king
of Hero World, our friend,
Ultimate Card Burn.
When Card Burn, Card Rhino,
and Card Serpent
are sent from the field
to the drop zone,
Ultimate Card Burn can do a
direct ride from the deck!
His power is 12,000 and
his defense is 8,000!
That makes him one of
the strongest cards!
Plus he's got a critical of
three and a double attack!
So what do you think, guys?
Think you can open
up one of these?
(together)
You'll never know until you try!
♪
Next time, with the fate
of the world on the line,
Kyoya reveals his dark ambition.
And when Tasuku and Kiri unite
and head to the enemy's lair,
they find a surprise
waiting for them.
Next episode,
The Shadow of Demise!
Join us for a Buddyfight!