Get ready for
a cool, new card game
that connects to
a parallel universe.
Special cards
act as portals
bringing monsters to earth
to become Buddies
with humans.
And through
friendship and courage,
help them take on
fight challenges.
It's called
"Buddyfight."
We got the gauge!
Time to let 'er rip, Drum.
(groans)
Magician Drum's Megablast...
Bunker!
This is gonna hurt.
(groans)
♪
Woo!
Abracadabra,
Grendel's out of there.
Gao has caused four
damage points to Raremaro,
and it's still his turn!
Is this the end for Seng Ad's
illustrious president?
You're next, Burning Fist.
Go and attack the fighter.
(grunting)
Okay, Axia, go zap 'em!
With pleasure.
But I won't be as gentle
as I was with you!
Shocking, no?
Drum, the glory's
all yours, man.
(grunts)
Drill Blaster!
♪
(Raremaru shrieks)
‐Stop right there.
Yeah, stay back.
Don't you know
what this place is?
You're at Sengoku
Academy, little girl.
Oh, maybe she
communicates
telepathetically.
I'm having a vision
of her going away.
Listen, Rouga Aragami
brought a young boy
here last night.
Tell me where he is.
Guess there's bad
reception here.
Nothing comes free.
You've gotta win
a Buddyfight
if you want us to
answer your questions.
Huh?
Where'd she go?
Maybe she does have
telepathetic powers.
(groans)
Where is the boy?
I‐‐I really don't know.
That figures.
Dark Buddy Skill on.
The hair‐raising
showdown between
Aibo and Sengoku continues.
For all you newbies out there,
let's recap the matches
we've had so far.
The first match
paired off Sen Cad's
Rouga Aragami and
Aibo's Tetsuya Kurodake.
♪
I'll get you, and
your little monster, too.
Drill Bunker!
But I was having
so much fun!
Swirling Darkness
penetrates Beleth.
Aragami's overwhelming
skills proved too much
for Tetsuya who busted a move
right out of the contest, yo.
The second match pitted
Kemura, the Frog Man,
against Aibo's
Genma Todoroki.
It's basically
a magic dragon eraser.
Special properties
in the steel let
the user destroy them
with just one blow.
Cha‐ching!
How do I get one of those?
Aibo Middle School's
number one ranked fighter,
Genma, was taken down, but...
it was only 'cause
of a hate card.
The third match saw
Kemura stay in the field
after accepting a challenge
from Aibo's Kazane Fujimiya.
♪
Release the Raptor Blades!
The Frog Man was
determined to win
his next match
on his own merits,
but instead he was
carried away by the Wind,
aka, Kazane.
The fourth match
was between our own,
Zanya Kisaragi, and
Sen Cad's Ninja Kanahebi.
♪
Five Heavenly Swords,
Onimaru, Twisted
Spirit Purification!
Zanya dominated
the Katana World Showdown,
ending the Kanahebi Ninja's
shot in the victory here.
And in the fifth
and most recent match,
Gao Mikado shocked us all
by destroying Sen Cad's
student council
president Raremaro
with a Magic World deck.
As it stands,
Aibo has three
players left
and Sengoku has two.
(grunts)
‐My stomach!
‐Are you all right?
Something cramping
your style, yo?
It's just that I
haven't eaten all day.
I packed tons
of club sandwiches,
but when the blimp crash
landed in the woods,
they got all squished.
Don't tell me
you're just hungry.
(groans)
What a horrifying waste!
Okay, that's it.
It's my turn to get
a little hangry.
Spies need food, too.
It's no surprise.
None of us have
eaten anything
since breakfast.
Well, we can't go into
battle on empty stomachs.
What do you think?
Do you wanna go
grab something?
Let's hit the snack bar.
But aren't you
fighting next?
I'll go in your place.
Buddyfight is my food.
Plus I had
a granola bar earlier.
Please, Blade, can I?
Fine, puppy dog eyes.
All right!
It looks like Aibo's
decided that Kazane
will suit up
for the next match.
She knocked Kemura out
of the event last time.
Let's see if she can keep
her winning streak alive.
And her mysterious
opponent from Sen Cad
fighting for the
first time today...
is Shosetsu Kirisame.
I wondered when that guy
was gonna start playing.
How is it?
Can you see me?
Yeah, I can see perfectly.
Now we can go get
some chow without
worrying about things.
Thanks a lot for
hooking us up.
Okay, Drum, time to
get us some fuel.
I bet they have
all kinds of pudding!
(giggles)
Oh, maybe they'll have pizza!
Yeah!
Buddyfight!
Oh, yeah.
‐Time to raise the flag.
Buddy Skill on.
I fight for Dungeon World.
And I for Legend World.
What gives?
Where's his Buddy, yo?
Tets, Buddies come in
all shapes and sizes.
Try looking closely at his belt.
‐What do you see?
‐His belt?
You mean that item?
His sword?
Of course Buddies
aren't always
gonna be monsters.
Some are items from
famous legends or myths.
But, I'll admit,
this is my first time
seeing one.
It never breaks, dents,
rusts, or shatters.
It's the fabled
Demon Sword of Legend World.
It's said that by
winning and surviving
countless battles,
the sword somehow
came to life.
I am the Immortal
Sword, Durandal.
Hear that?
He's got an item
for a Buddy.
Man, I wish I was
fighting him.
Focus on the food.
Kazane will go first!
Let's get started.
Charge and draw.
I call Gummy Slime
to the center position.
♪
Gummy‐my!
Gummy, attack the fighter!
♪
End of move.
In your face!
Your move.
Draw.
Charge and draw.
My turn.
I will pay one gauge
and call Knights
of the Round Table,
King Arthur,
to the right.
♪
Knights of the Round Table,
Gawain, go to the left position.
♪
And I equip Famous
Sword, Hrunting.
♪
Now, King Arthur,
Gawain, unite
in a link attack.
With a knight's
code and honor.
Yes, sire.
When King Arthur
and Gawain combine
forces in a link attack,
they both gain
the ability to penetrate.
♪
Oh, no!
‐Protect the kingdom!
(shouts)
Hrunting, let's
cut in on the act.
(grunts)
(Kazane shouts)
♪
End of move.
Incredibly, Shosetsu
stripped Kazane
of seven life points
in just one turn.
That was rather fierce.
Are you all right, Kazane?
I'm super.
That's some
serious power.
I feel like his
sword is looking at me.
Us Kisaragis can
sense these things.
Yo, is it looking at me?
Don't worry
about it, Tets.
What they're picking
up on isn't the sword,
it's something about
that Shosetsu guy.
No matter what
my opponent's like,
I gotta give it my best.
That's the way I roll.
Okay, it's my turn.
Time to kick it.
Draw.
Charge and draw.
I call Fate
Skeleton to the right,
Scout, Criticizing
Kirwa to the left,
and Thunder Spartis
to the center.
♪
Skeleton, feel it
down to your bones.
Attack Gawain!
♪
Thunder Spartis,
attack King Arthur.
♪
Okay, Kirwa,
attack the fighter.
♪
End of move.
You go, girl.
She's not giving up.
And with Thunder Spartis'
9,000 defense at her center,
she's got a chance.
♪
Hah.
Gawain to the left.
And Galahad to the right.
Shosetsu has called
two units out
for his offensive,
but Thunder Spartis
is ready and waiting
to pounce.
I choose to return
Hrunting to my hand
and Buddy Call.
I equip Immortal
Sword, Durandal.
He switches swords
like I change socks.
It's a Legend World thing.
Some items can be
returned to your hand
when you switch items.
Galahad, Gawain,
link attack with me.
‐Right.
This threefold
link attack combo
will increase his
defensive to 13,000!
(grunting)
Gawain, penetrate!
(screams)
♪
Oh, no, Spartis!
Morgan le Fay!
(Kazane shrieks)
♪
Game over.
Winner: Shosetsu Kirisame.
And just like that,
Kazane's been eliminated
from the contest!
I'm here, Kazane.
Are you all right?
Yeah, I'm fine.
But I don't get it.
He doesn't seem to enjoy
Buddyfighting at all.
That Shosetsu's
a skilled swordsman.
I'll go next.
We'll show him, Z.
Oh, man, I'm so hungry!
I think I see the
counter over there.
What's with the crazy line up?
This will take forever.
We don't have
time for this!
We're in a major hurry.
Any chance we can
get our lunch first?
You know what to do
if you want something.
You have to beat us
in a Buddy fight.
Okay, if that's
how it's gotta be.
I'm tongue‐tied.
Both schools now have
two players remaining.
And it looks like
Aibo's sending out
Zanya Kisaragi
for the next match.
Let's hope he continues
his victorious ways.
Sen Cad sticks with
their winning recipe,
keeping Shosetsu
Kirisame in the field.
Wait and see what
I'm capable of, Rouga.
It's time you realized
who is truly worthy
of being given
that dark power.
Me!
Not that little kid you
brought here last night.
(grunts)
Fail.
That's it.
You're going down, Rookie.
But I'm starving.
How many of these guys
do I have to beat anyway?
♪
Strike down bandits
with Scuffle Card play.
Luminize.
Behold, Great Oedo
Criminal Arrest Record!
A thousand swords
defeating the enemy
with a thousand vows.
Luminize.
Fortress of Swords.
Buddyfight!
‐Raise the flag!
I fight for Katana World,
Tsukikage.
Nin!
Buddy Skill on.
And I for Legend World.
Shosetsu will go first.
Charge and draw.
I call to the center
Knights of the Round Table,
Percival.
♪
Percival, attack the fighter.
It's my duty.
A knight welcomes battle.
(grunts)
♪
End of move.
Rouga, I saw you once
before you became
a student here at Sen Cad.
It was a long time ago
when I was training
alone in the sea of
trees below Mt Fuji.
You couldn't have known
because I kept out of sight,
but I was amazed.
And what I saw
I will never,
ever forget.
What is that?
(alarms blare)
This is a restricted area.
Crimson Slash!
I've never seen
a Buddyfighter
like him before.
Most unusual.
Somehow he's making the
force of the cards real.
It appears so.
Is that possible?
I would do anything
to have that power.
‐Cyber Analyze!
‐Hm?
I'll pay one gauge
and discard one
Ninja Arts guard
from my hand,
and then draw two
cards from the deck.
He's added cards
to his hand
using Shiden's ability.
I Buddy Call
to the center,
Nanomachine Ninja, Tsukikage.
And another
Tsukikage to the left.
♪
Nin, nin!
Shiden, use your stuff
to attack Percival.
(grunts)
♪
Now, both Tsukikages,
attack the fighter!
♪
End of move.
After just dropping
four life points,
Shosetsu doesn't seem
to be phased in the least.
Then, months later
when you first appeared
at Sen Cad, I couldn't
believe you were the same
person I had seen before.
Drill Bunker!
(scream)
I had no proof that
you were somehow
making the power
from your cards real.
But there was only one
way for me to find out.
And that was to
fight you myself.
Great Magician, Merlin,
to the right.
♪
Merlin's ability,
Incubus Blood!
By paying one gauge
and discarding one
hero card, Shosetsu
can now look at the top
five cards of his deck
and add up to two spell
or item cards
to his hand.
I Buddy Call!
Here comes the sword.
Watch out, Zanya!
It's way strong.
He's on his own
now, Kazane.
I equip Immortal
Sword, Durandal.
Whoa, that sword.
Maybe Zanya's right,
there is something
weird about it.
Knights of the Round
Table, King Arthur
to the left.
♪
King Arthur, Merlin,
link attack the Tsukikage
in the center.
Feel the power
of penetrate
from thy king's sword!
Victory!
♪
Over to you.
End of move.
My chance to confront you
came soon enough, Rouga.
Do you really think
you're the strongest
Buddyfighter around these parts?
Hard to say, now that
you're here, that is.
The only way to get my
respect is to fight me.
Bada‐bing bada‐boom.
In one brilliant move,
Shosetsu reduced
Zanya's life points
and destroyed Shiden,
the monster that can
adds cards to his hand.
Hmph.
What, you didn't think that
I could do power plays too?
I call to the right Stealth
Ninja, Kirikakure Saizo.
♪
And by choosing
to pay one gauge,
I equip Five Heavenly
Swords, Onimaru.
♪
Tsukikage, I'm
leaving Merlin to you.
Saizo, follow me.
Right.
Nin!
This is my legend!
Yah!
♪
Equipment change, Prydwen.
What?
Divine Protection, Prydwen
lets you reduce
damage by two
if you pay two gauge.
I guess I have no
choice but to use it.
Final phase.
Lethal Formation!
♪
He keeps changing
his equipped item
during the fight.
It's his strategy.
If that's the case,
then I should use
Shooting Star.
Set.
♪
You opened my eyes.
You were more powerful
than I'd ever imagined, Rouga.
You're very strong.
I admit with the
cards in my hand
I have no chance of winning.
As I see it,
there is no point
for me to continue
this fight between us.
No point?
Instead, I pledge
myself to serve you.
I call to the right...
Knight of the Round
Table, Gawain.
♪
Equipment change.
Durandal.
King Arthur, Gawain,
attack the fighter.
Together, brothers in arms.
Until the end!
♪
Say good night!
I cast!
Art of Body Replacement.
Not yet!
(grunts)
♪
End of move.
I shadowed you, Rouga,
so I could gain
your knowledge
and power for myself.
Shosetsu did it again.
Zanya's down, but not out.
He's still got Saizo
and Tsukikage in play.
Not only that, Five
Heavenly Swords, Onimaru
has three critical points.
Zanya's victory might
just be around the corner.
Ah!
We'll do an
all‐out attack.
‐Ensnare the warrior!
‐Nin!
Equipment change, Prydwen.
Nin!
♪
Reduce the damage,
but with that maneuver
he's used up all his gauge.
Hide in the mist and
cut through the shadows,
mutation soul, I cast...
Holy Grail!
Shosetsu used
the Fountain of Youth
counter spell to
cancel Saizo's attack.
Come on, Z!
You can do it!
Beat this guy!
Right.
Onimaru!
I cast...
Holy Grail!
Another well‐timed
counter spell
means that our
Sen Cad fighter
survived the turn
with no damage.
He had two of them?
End of move.
Rouga, you insulted my honor.
To bring someone
like him into
competition with me.
♪
I will train him here.
And don't even think
of interfering.
♪
Why didn't you choose me?
Or anyone else from
Sen Cad, for that matter?
Why give all the
attention to a player
with no experience?!
Equipment change.
Durandal.
King Arthur, Gawain,
attack the fighter.
You've made a huge
mistake, Rouga.
You'll see.
And now I'm going
to prove it to you.
Fourteen fights.
They better be worth it.
Huh?
What's our student council
vice president doing here?
Hey!
Wait!
(grunts)
♪
Brother, no!
I commend thee.
You fought valiantly.
I cast!
What's this?
Art of Body Replacement.
(groans)
♪
You've fallen
right into my trap.
I pay three gauge to
activate Lethal Formation.
Secret Sword,
Shooting Star!
Hya!
(shrieks)
♪
Did you see that?
He destroyed the item
using Secret Sword,
Shooting Star, and
gave him three damage!
Check it, yo,
Zanya's the man.
Forgot what I said, didn't you?
Maybe.
At the beginning of the fight,
I told you Durandal
never breaks, dents,
rusts, or shatters.
There's a reason why
it can't be destroyed.
It's an Immortal Sword.
It didn't break.
It's true.
Durandal's as
powerful as they come.
(screams)
Zanya!
Game over.
Winner: Shosetsu Kirisame.
And there it is.
That should wake Mikado up.
Maybe now he'll
get serious about
his fighting again.
Whoa, I never knew
fighting tactics
like this even existed.
I didn't believe
Rouga at first,
but if I study here
I just might become
stronger like he says.
Maybe even as strong as Gao.
So this is where
you've been hiding?
Uh?
Oh.
Miss Vice President.
What are you doing here?
There's something I've
been meaning to give to you.
But...isn't that...
She's around here somewhere.
‐No!
‐Huh?
Kiri!
It's time for‐‐
Tasuku and Gao's‐‐
‐Card of the day!
And today we have
the terrifying
Thunder Knights Leader,
Kommandeur Fahne.
He's the head of
the Thunder Knights.
And I hear he's got
an awesome attack
with lightning speed!
That's right.
He adds one
critical point to all
Thunder Knights cards.
And he gives all
of them the ability
called "Move."
Not to mention, it's able
to enhance itself, too.
This guy'd help
anyone build a powerful
Thunder Knights deck.
So, what do you
think, guys?
You think you can
open one of these?
You'll never know
until you try!
♪
Next time, Sofia Sakharov
tempts Kiri with the power
of the Dark Core.
Meanwhile, me and Gao
square off against Shosetsu,
and we get in
over our heads.
Next episode,
"Gao's Buddy Skill is On!"
It's gonna be real!