Do you have what it
takes to Buddyfight?
Choose your favorite world
and use special cards
to summon its powerful
monsters into reality.
Challenge other fighters,
and Buddy Call your
toughest ally to fight
by your side.
Get ready to
raise the flag.
♪
We now have an
important announcement
from our tournament sponsor.
Please welcome
Mr. Kyoya Gaen.
Amazingly with all
the excitement,
the Gaen Cup is
already at the finals.
And this will serve
as the last surprise
you'll see from me.
Get ready for
the pairing cards
for the final round.
The pairing what?
The first game will
be Sofia Sakharov
versus Tetsuya Kurodake.
The second game will be
Rouga Aragami versus
Zanya Kisaragi.
And the final game
will be Purgatory Knight,
aka Tasuku Ryuenji,
aka my boyfriend,
versus Gao Mikado.
This is the official
order of the fights.
That Kyoya's bad news.
It's totally obvious
he's up to something
by arranging the
fights in this way.
I say we keep rolling
with the punches.
I just don't trust this guy.
I feel it.
Kyoya Gaen is
plotting something, bro.
Huh?
♪
I don't understand.
It's unusual.
Why would Kyoya want
to determine all of
the match‐ups in advance?
It's clear he has more
than entertainment
on his mind.
(magical whirring)
I couldn't agree more.
He's planning something,
and I'm pretty sure
we're not gonna like it.
Yes, but as the tournament
sponsor, his decision stands.
Huh?
Where did Kemura go?
I don't know, but he
sure left in a hurry.
It's a big campus.
I hope he doesn't get lost.
Come on, it's this way.
Do you think you're
gonna make it this time?
Don't know.
Can't hold it much
longer, though, kem.
Must hurry!
You must go.
The party is
in your honor.
And don't forget
your favorite hero
Captain Answer
will be there.
Really?
Answer is coming
to my party?
Well, a bronze
statue of him anyway.
(chuckles)
You're so out of touch.
‐Huh?
It's Magoroku Shido
and his father.
Just stay calm.
Walking your dog, Genma?
You should really
try and show
a little more respect
for your father, Shido.
He may do some things
you don't like, but it's
probably for your own good.
It's none of your business.
And I don't recall
asking for your advice.
The only person
I've ever listened to
on these things is the
great Captain Answer.
You Seifukai think
you know everything.
Come along, Daddy.
We'll be late
for my party.
Oh, goodie!
I knew you'd come around.
Now I can see why he
gets under your skin.
He's getting worse.
He still believes
winning's everything,
and that those who
lose are worthless.
It's why he teamed
up with Kyoya Gaen
in the first place.
He won't listen to reason.
♪
We're running out of time.
Tasuku's facing off
against Gao Mikado tomorrow.
We need to act.
It's in everyone's
best interest.
Then you've decided
to put the plan
into action?
Yes, finally
the wait is over.
Tonight we're going to
take back the Buddy Police.
Just remember to be
cautious, Commander I.
These people are dangerous.
And when the time comes,
you must call upon
Captain Answer.
I'm positive it's this way.
We've already looked
everywhere else.
I'll have to call you back.
(toilet flushes)
Uhh!
Oh, sorry!
Are you okay?
Yes, I...
I'm fine!
If you say so.
Oh, me gonna burst, kem.
What's this?
I don't believe it.
This is Captain
Answer's Core Gadget.
What's it doing
at our school?
You don't think
something's
happened to him?
My guess is he lost it
while secretly taking in
the matches at
the tournament.
Remember, he is
a Buddyfighter after all.
He's gonna lose his
mind when realizes
his Core Gadget's gone.
That is, if he
hasn't already.
Hmm.
We must get it back to
him as soon as possible.
The thing is, how do
we go about doing that
when his identity
is unknown?
I hear you.
He did play a key role
in founding
the Buddy Police.
Maybe we should go
and give it to them.
I'm sure someone there will
know how to contact him.
You have a point.
Demongodol and I
will go with you,
just in case.
Yeah, we'll help
keep it safe.
Kemura and Sylph
go too, please.
Road trip!
Since ancient times,
friends have united
for the common good.
Today we march
to empower a hero!
‐Yeah!
My opponent should've
been disqualified.
The truth is that
amateur Gremlin
built me a deck that
wasn't at all suited
for my superior strategy.
He failed.
That's right,
you tell them, son.
Nothing's more important
than having the right
deck to play with.
I know most of you will
agree that it should
be me fighting in
the finals tomorrow.
Not so sure about that.
(chuckles)
You're one to talk.
You weren't much help
out there either, okay?
Oh, yeah?
Why don't you chew
on this, you wannabe!
(struggling)
Stop this minute!
Leave my boy alone,
you mangy rascal!
♪
All right, Nobari
doesn't suspect a thing.
The time is now.
‐Roger that.
I've disabled
the security protocols
on Nobari's computer.
Nice work.
♪
That's just perfect.
They're closed?
I didn't know that
preventing crime
was a nine‐to‐five job.
♪
Well, someone thinks
a lot of himself.
♪
If Nobari and Kyoya Gaen
are really working together,
then there's bound
to be some kind
of evidence linking
them to each other
in here somewhere.
For our plan to work,
we'll need some proof
of Nobari's corruption.
If there's any chance
of changing Tasuku's mind...
Then we must take back
control of the Buddy Police.
(squeaking)
Huh?
Just as I thought.
Now let's see what
he's hiding on here.
Ah!
No, wait, you can't!
But I've been
rehearsing all day.
She'll ruin everything!
Huh?
We're busted.
♪
He's getting away.
You're on your own, guys.
You gave us all
the time we needed.
Thanks, Card Burn.
Okay, nobody move.
If you so much as
scratch your nose,
you're fired!
(gasps)
Examiner Shido, come!
This had better not
be a false alarm!
You're abandoning me
at my own party?
S‐‐s‐‐shakedown!
(wailing)
Watch out for the floor.
I just waxed it and
it's kinda slippery.
(gasps)
So it's you, Commander I.
I thought you might
be beh‐‐h‐‐hind this!
(Gallows chuckles)
Stop that laughing.
Consider this your notice.
Your days of running
the Buddy Police are over.
Ow!
Oh?
That so?
Well, take this!
Excellent, now that's
showing initiative, sir.
Bring it on, tough guy.
This isn't good.
Come in, Card Burn.
We need backup.
(grunts)
Great, it's broken.
What else could go wrong?
Well, our legs
aren't broken.
Let's use the stairs.
Yeah, stairs, kem.
(groans)
He's kidding, right?
He expects us
to climb way up there?
Tampering with the Fuji
Mine security footage?
Illegal trafficking
of monsters?
Doctored crime reports?
Records of anonymous
cash deposits?
More than enough here.
Get out of there!
Leaving right now.
Going somewhere, Stella?
(gasps)
I think that
belongs to me.
(wails)
No!
This is the end of the line.
Your criminal shenanigans
end today.
The Buddy Police are back.
(whimpers)
I knew that it
couldn't last.
Some great party
this turned out to be.
‐Stella!
‐You all right?
Take this, quickly!
(panting)
Give it back!
Huh?
♪
Nice moves, pal.
All in a day's work.
You ninny!
What kind of fool keeps
a record of such things?
I've had to keep track
of all your schemes
somehow, didn't I?
If they expose
our wrongdoings,
we'll be ruined, ruined!
Well, can't you
do something?
(chuckles)
It's curtain
for the Sh‐‐Shidos!
Nobody will ever
get the best of us!
I'll save you, Father.
Disaster Force, activate.
♪
‐No.
‐Sir?
Look at your hair.
It's all wrong for you.
Get ready to witness
my true power.
We're back live
with Paruko Nanana,
your beautiful guide
to the world of Buddyfight.
I'm here at Team
Balle du Soleil's
victory party.
As you can see,
everyone's pretty
pumped up after today's
big semi‐final win.
With the pairings for
tomorrow's final match‐ups
recently revealed,
let's see how the players
are feeling about their chances.
(chewing)
We're not haters, yo.
We roll with
any opponent, but‐‐
But we don't think it's
cool for anyone to tell us
who we gotta fight, you dig?
I don't trust
that Kyoya Gaen.
It's obvious that
he's setting us up.
He has a plan.
You keep saying that,
but what is it?
There's no point
worrying about it, you guys.
How can you be so
calm about this?
I mean, you're fighting
the great Tasuku Ryuenji.
Don't let your
fear control you.
We are Buddyfighters, after all.
Our skill should
do the talking,
don't you think?
The kid's right.
You gotta beat your opponent
to win, whoever it is.
Now that's settled,
let's get out snack on.
And recharge our mojo
so we can win this.
‐To victory!
(munching)
Hey, you scarfed
down all of it!
(chuckles)
If you're hungry,
there's a big octopus
right there.
Tako‐chu!
He's not an octopus!
And he's not food!
Takosuke, run for cover!
Tako‐chu!
We'll check back
with Paruko
later in the broadcast.
But first...
Please join me in
welcoming all three
members of Team Purgatory
to our studio.
I bet you can't wait
to hear from team leader
Tasuku Ryu‐‐
I mean Mr. Purgatory Knight.
So, your fans know you
as the Buddy
Police boy wonder,
but what they're
dying to know is why
you hid your
identity from them.
Sorry, but I have no comment.
Uh, really?
Not even a few words?
Uh, maybe your teammates
would like to say something.
Anybody?
Someone?
I don't have
time for this.
Huh?
I...
(nervous chuckle)
The enigmatic
Team Purgatory.
Stay tuned for
tomorrow's weather.
♪
You have nowhere to run.
Give up already!
♪
What are you doing?
Just take the laptop
and get out of here.
I won't leave you.
Not until you
and Stella are safe.
Do you really think
you're any match
for my power?
We've got company!
Not interrupting, are we?
The roof?
Let me guess,
the view was just
too spectacular to miss.
Get lost or we'll have you
arrested for trespassing.
I almost didn't
recognize you.
What's going on here?
Stay back, kids.
It isn't safe!
I didn't give you
permission to talk.
Guillotine Cutter!
(explosion)
(groans)
Oh, no!
‐The laptop.
Don't let them get it!
Come to papa!
(gasps)
Gotcha.
It looks like your
little plan has failed.
We'll have to destroy
his core in a Buddyfight.
It's too risky.
He can make the power
of the cards real.
You can't fight him.
We should go, now.
Not yet.
You're not really threatening
the Buddy Police, are you?
You?
Haven't we been
over this, Seifukai?
The only person
I'll listen to
is Captain Answer.
He can be as
stubborn as he wants,
but I have an idea.
Here's the deal, losers,
you either fight me or leave.
Who's that jerk
think he's talking to?
Hang on.
What happened to Genma?
Nobody move.
(whimpers)
Oh, dear.
Guess they found us.
The wind carries
all the answers.
I am the one who
answers for justice.
They call me Captain Answer!
He really was
coming to my party!
‐Huh?
‐Hey, that's Genma.
You're not him.
Is this some kind
of twisted Seifukai joke?
You're mistaken.
Magoroku Shido,
you have welcomed
a dark and evil power into
your life which you now
plan on using to harm others.
It is inexcusable.
I, Captain Answer,
will straighten out
your corrupted morals.
You'll do no such thing.
You're just a cheap imposter
claiming to be
someone you're not,
and for that
I'll punish you.
It has been said
since ancient times
that the more
frightened a dog is,
the more he barks.
Justice is within
one's heart!
Luminize,
Shining Answer!
To defeat and humiliate
all fools who cross me.
Dark Luminize,
Black Cloud of
Endless Doom.
‐Time to raise the flag.
I fight for Hero World!
I fight for
Darkness Dragon World.
Oh, no!
It's missing!
But how?
This is awful.
What'll I do?
Where oh where can
my Core Gadget be?
Charge and...
draw!
We'll see how excited
you are after I defeat you.
I call the First Warrior,
Einder, to the right.
And a Second Warrior,
Zweider, to the left.
Einder.
Zweider.
And now, Answer Question.
I ask, is the next card
a spell or a monster?
My answer... a spell!
Justice Will Prevail.
A‐plus!
(screams)
Your friend's
talking to himself.
He's just using
the ability on
Captain Answer's card.
When it's played,
the fighter must predict
if the top card
in the deck is
a spell or a monster.
And if he chooses correctly,
he can attack twice.
Einder, spring into action
and attack Gallows.
Meteor Blast.
Zweider, attack the fighter.
Zweider Spear!
Yeah, right.
I'll just cast my
awesome Death Shield.
(Zweider screams)
(laughs)
Teach you to mess with me.
The only one who needs to
learn a lesson here is you.
Believe me, this will hurt me
more than it'll hurt you,
but it's time you grow up!
(grunts)
(Magoruko shrieks)
Ah!
My poor boy.
And lucky for you,
it's a double attack.
(grunts)
♪
Oh, the humanity!
I have been traumatized.
Why would anyone do that
to this beautiful face?
(chuckles)
Stop that laughing!
I call a second
Death Ruler, Gallows
to the center.
(Gallows chuckles)
Both Gallows attack Answer!
Double head Gallows!
I cast...
Justice Will Prevail!
♪
That's a counterspell
that increases both
power and defense!
And also gives him
a choice of counterattack.
(grunts)
♪
Captain Answer,
don't take it easy on him.
Use your compass gun,
a Recorder Javelin.
He probably doesn't
even know that those
weapons are an option.
Huh?
Come on, son, stay strong!
This is unheard of.
I can't believe that
things have gotten
to this point.
(groans)
All I can do is hope
Kyoya has a way out of this.
It's late.
Yeah, sorry, sir.
I need your help.
What's the problem?
Interesting.
I expected them
to try something.
Don't worry,
leave everything to me.
I've planned for this.
Thanks for letting me know.
And keep up the good work.
Thank you, Master Gaen.
You know what to do.
Duh.
Seven Swords!
Why me?
Come on, my boy.
You can't give up now!
It's been said
since ancient times
that good medicine
tastes bitter.
Prepare yourself.
(whimpers)
You're gonna hit me
again, aren't you?
Looks like Genma‐‐
I mean, Captain Answer
has once again used
his Answer Question
ability and gained
a double attack.
And Mr. Whiney Pants only
has four life remaining.
You gotta help me, please!
Don't touch me.
Time for your medicine!
Frost Wall,
Nevel Vans.
♪
Where'd that mist come from?
I can't see.
(groans)
♪
I thought you
were someone else.
Here, they're
trying to get this.
That's it?
(shrieks)
Hey, why'd you do that?
I'm just following
the boss's orders.
Oh, really?
Me again.
What's all this about?
I let you head up
the Buddy Police
for one reason:
to help me acquire
Tasuku Ryuenji.
And now that he is
a member of Disaster,
you are no longer
of any use to me.
But‐‐but you're wrong.
I'm still necessary.
And besides, if I'm exposed
and an investigation is made,
then you'll be at risk!
You don't honestly
believe that, do you?
I'm quite safe,
I assure you.
You're the only one
who'll be ruined.
Mm.
(gasps)
He thanks you
for your service.
Ah!
Stay away!
Help!
(shrieks)
We're gonna fall!
(screaming)
‐Magoroku!
‐Come on, Shido.
Use your Buddy Skill!
Because my buddy
never gave me one!
I keep meaning to do that.
I guess he can have it,
if he makes it.
(screaming)
♪
Prisoner is secure.
It is you in there,
isn't it, Genma?
Once again,
you are mistaken.
(laughs)
That was one
dramatic rescue.
Yeah, they don't come
any closer than that.
Good save, kem.
All I can say is...
we owe Captain Answer
our deepest gratitude.
Huh?
♪
There will no doubt be
a thorough investigation
into Nobari's
criminal dealings.
And even though he was
an unwitting accomplice,
I'm afraid
Examiner Shido
won't be able to avoid
prosecution either.
Thank you both.
Because our mission
was successful,
Tasuku Ryuenji can
now return to his
rightful place
alongside us.
‐Sir.
♪
We'll be waiting, Tasuku.
You belong with us.
It may take a little time
for you to figure that out,
but there is goodness in
you, and I know in my heart
that you'll make
the right choice.
♪
It's time for‐‐
Tasuku and Gao's‐‐
Card of the Day!
Today we're gonna
tell you all about
our favorite hero
named Captain Answer.
Pay one gauge to guess
if the top card in your
deck is a monster or a spell.
If you guess right,
you get a little bonus.
He means Captain Answer
will gain a double attack
during that turn.
Now we can be just like the
man who answers for justice.
Pretty cool, if you ask me.
So, what do you think, guys?
You think you can
open up one of these?
You'll never know
until you try!
♪
Next time, the final round
of the Gaen Cup begins.
And Tetsuya better look out.
Even with the help
of his team,
Sofia may be
too tough to beat.
Next episode:
Gaen Cup Final Round!
Tetsuya's Choice!
Join us for a Buddyfight!