♪
Do you have what it
takes to Buddyfight?
Choose your favorite world
and use special cards
to summon its powerful
monsters into reality.
Challenge other fighters and
buddy call your toughest ally
to fight by your side.
Get ready to
raise the flag!
Welcome back to our exciting
coverage of the Gaen Cup.
The third and
deciding match
that will name our
opening round winner
is about to get started.
Alright.
Remember what
we talked about.
How could I forget?
You only told me
like ten times.
What's wrong, Tetsuya?
You don't look
so good, man.
If it's something I said
about your dancing, I'm sorry.
What could
possibly be wrong?
At least he
won his fight.
‐Cheer up, Z.
‐Nin.
Actually, if you
want to know‐‐
Zip it, A‐Dog,
it's personal, you dig.
(all gasping)
Tets puts it all out
there during his fight,
so his vibe hits the
mat after any big match.
I think we should give the
little homie some space
to wind down and chill.
Yeah, come on, guys!
Drum and I need
to go and get ready
for our match anyway.
‐About that.
‐Who are we fighting?
Yeah, I wonder
who Team Goddess
is going to be
throwing at us next.
Nin.
If you ask me, they're at
a really big advantage.
We don't know their fighter,
but they know all about Gao.
Doesn't that make
you guys nervous?
I don't think we
need to worry about that.
Yeah, bro, we
built Gao's deck
so he could fight
the way he wants
no matter who
his opponent is.
Worrying just
isn't his style.
Like my father used
to always tell me,
you got to fight
like nobody's watching.
Okay, I guess
he could be right.
So, ready to win this?
‐Yeah!
I know it's hard, Tets, but
you got to forget about her.
Hmm.
Come on, let's
see that smile.
Hmm?
Your team needs you now.
We should try to be
there and support them.
That's why
you're my A‐Dog.
♪
Good luck out there!
‐Thanks!
We should get ourselves
to the Buddy pit.
Yeah, I can't wait!
Hmm?
♪
(gasps)
Are you okay?
Hmm?
Did you see something?
Tell me.
I'll be right back.
Hey, wait!
What about
the tournament?
It's a battle
for survival.
The team that wins
this next game
will move on to the
second round of the Gaen Cup.
You can do it!
Show 'em why they call
you the Mighty Sun Fighter!
You're confident.
I'm still wondering who
he'll be fighting against.
Balle du Soleil's
fighter, Gao Mikado,
is ready and
waiting for action,
but his opponent from Team
Goddess is nowhere to be seen.
According to
tournament rules,
if they don't show soon,
Gao will win by default.
This isn't the way anyone
dreams of getting a victory.
Oh, I don't
know about that.
A win is a win,
I always say.
No.
He would never
think like that.
Yeah, well,
he's different.
(roaring)
How much longer are we gonna
have to wait for these guys?
I was gonna build the
suspense a little longer,
but, honestly,
Team Goddess' fighter
has been under your
noses the whole time.
‐What?
‐What are you talking about?
Where is she?
(grunts)
That's right,
ladies and gentlemen!
Your opponent for this round
is none other than me.
Now we can get this
knockout game started.
Tako‐chu.
Oh, and don't worry, I'll
still be announcing too.
‐Huh?
‐What the‐‐
Do you think she Buddyfights
the same way that she talks?
I didn't even think
she knew how to fight.
I've never seen her play,
but I heard Paruko's
the best fighter
in the school
broadcasting club.
Well, she must be good
if they're letting
her go up against Gao.
Yeah.
♪
I wonder where Baku is.
Retsu, wait up.
All the way from
Andromeda, I shine!
Luminize!
Falling Twinkle Star!
The most
powerful deck ever
blazing a path
towards the future!
Luminize!
Explosive Dragon Fang!
Say it like you
mean it, people!
You know you want
to see me Buddyfight!
(crowd cheering)
‐Time to raise the flag.
I fight for Dragon World.
I'm with Hero World.
Tako‐chu!
FYI, Hero World has all
sorts of cool monsters.
Everything from
stylish aliens
to powerful robots that
can combine their forms.
You can have
the first turn.
This is gonna be weird.
Charge and draw.
I call Systemic Dagger
Dragon to the center.
Now, attack Paruko.
Gao doesn't
waste any time
sending out his first
punishing attack!
End of move.
Wait, you mean
she's gonna do
the play by play
of her own fight?
Now, Paruko has her first
turn of the tournament.
She calls to the right,
the first mighty warrior from
the Quartet Five, Einder,
and to the center position,
she calls the
Third Warrior, Dreider.
Einder.
Dreider.
Okay, Einder, attack
Systemic Dagger Dragon!
Einder.
♪
(roars)
Dreider,
you're next!
Attack the fighter!
Dreider Shield!
Destroy!
(grunting)
End of move.
You know, you're
actually pretty good.
Both players have eight
life points left,
and Gao's preparing
for his second turn.
Hey, isn't this‐‐
Hey, coach!
Look at the new
deck I built.
I've been
waiting, Baku.
Well, aren't you
even gonna look at it?
Sure.
♪
I've been waiting, Baku.
Oh, hey, Retsu!
I didn't recognize
you for a second.
♪
I don't go by
that name anymore.
(gasps)
I'm a member of Disaster
and my name is Gremlin.
Draw.
Charge and draw.
Get ready, Paruko.
I call Thousand Rapier
to the left,
and buddy call
Drum to the right.
Welcome to the party.
(grunting)
I equip Dragon Blade
Drum Sword.
Look, he's setting
up the Gao Formation!
Will his predictability
be his downfall?
Here we go, Thousand.
Time to attack Dreider.
Yes, sir.
Huh?
Impero Veritas!
Drum, you go
attack Paruko.
With pleasure.
Thought you'd
never ask.
(grunting)
Crash Drill
Rad Bunker!
(screams)
(grunting)
Drum Sword!
(screams)
End of move.
Paruko's never found herself
in such a tough position.
Tako‐chu.
But that's okay,
because the real
fight is just beginning.
I draw.
Charge and draw.
With a dramatic cast,
I'll use It's About Time
I Got Serious! to draw two.
Now, from the far
reaches of outer space,
the one and only
Martin UFO, Takosuke!
Tako‐chu!
I buddy call
to the center.
Tako‐chu!
Player Paruko has
chosen to pay one gauge
so she can ride with her
favorite extraterrestrial.
The ride ability allows
a player to equip a monster
in the same way
one would an item.
Super UFO fusion!
Tako‐chu!
(grunts)
It's time for
Announcer Paruko Nanana's
surprise attack form!
Big deal.
She's always flying
around in that thing.
If Drum's finished
making comments,
Paruko is gonna pay one gauge
to activate the
Martian Zap Zap Beam ability.
Now this I really
got to see to believe.
A player says the
name of a card
and if their opponent
happens to have
the same card
in their hand,
they'll receive
two damage points.
♪
(energy charging)
You're gonna try to guess one of
the cards we have in our hand?
(laughing)
Good luck!
Hmm, my ability
may surprise you.
I've had the opportunity
of seeing Gao defeat many
powerful opponents before,
and at some point,
he always seems to use
Dragon Shield
to defend himself.
I'll explain.
It may seem he has the
dumb luck to help him draw
whatever card he wants
when he needs it,
but that's not so!
He often has a shield but
chooses not to use it.
Instead, leaving it in
his hand to the last second!
Because of that, I'm guessing
the card he has in his hand
is his ever so trusty
Green Dragon Shield!
(grunts)
Someone's about to
get zapped and it's you!
(screams)
No way!
I can't believe
she got it right, yo!
Don't get it twisted.
She has the edge.
She's called the play
on most of his fights.
Baku's not alone then.
There's someone else who knows a
lot about Gao's fighting style.
Hate to say I told you so.
Paruko attacks Gao using
the energy saving hero
of love and courage,
Solar Panel Man!
♪
I cast Green
Dragon Shield!
I don't want
to be predictable
but I really got to
increase my life points.
I cast
Or So The Dream I Had Went!
(gasps)
But that's a
counter spell!
Solar Kick!
(grunts)
How'd she damage him
when he defended himself?
That's not
the worst part.
Gao didn't even get
to gain any life points.
Martian Ray Blast!
(screams)
We're getting our
butts kicked.
Paruko always seems
one step ahead of us.
It's disappointing that
I couldn't be the one
to defeat
darling Gao myself,
but it's all turning
out as expected.
(giggling)
I had a feeling
the new addition
would prove to be
our team's secret weapon.
She knows everything
about the Sun Fighter.
♪
So, why don't you
become one of us?
What?
Darkness Dragon
World has some really
incredible cards
to choose from.
There are so many things
that I can teach you
to become a great
deck builder.
Why not become
my apprentice again?
♪
The deck that I
want to put together?
Why that's easy, Baks.
It's called
Darkness Dragon World.
But why do you
like that one?
Because it's a deck that no
one's ever built before.
I‐‐I‐‐
Wait, come back!
Why aren't we allowed
to hang out anymore?
I don't understand!
Don't go!
Please!
♪
Huh?
I call to the center,
Boomerang Dragon!
Let's go get
that dunny rat.
Go attack the
fighter, Drum!
I cast Justice
Will Prevail!
This spell increases
Takosuke's power
and defense by
3,000 and that's not all.
Counter attack!
You forgot about
my soul guard!
Thousand, why don't
you attack her instead?
I cast
I've Seen Through Your Moves!
Let fly,
Boomerang Dragon!
I'm going off like
a frog in a sock!
(grunting)
I'm the thunder
from Down Under!
What a move by Gao!
Time to unleash
Gao Formation Rebuilt!
Let's see her
counter this one.
I cast
I've Seen Through Your Moves!
(gasps)
End of move.
Gao's giving it his
best shot out there,
but he seems ill prepared
for Paruko's amazing skill
and her timely
counter spells.
We'll just see about that!
(sighs)
I forgot the match.
Here comes a second Martian Zap
Zap Beam from yours truly.
Unfortunately, somebody's
perfect formation
has a crucial flaw.
It's easy for his
opponents to guess
which cards he's holding up,
and do you know what's
even more predictable
than the outfit
he's wearing?
Boomerang Dragon just
returned to his hand.
You're probably the only person
who would realize that.
Who's ready for
some more zapping?
(screaming)
Now, Paruko's using Martian Ray
Gun on Thousand Rapier Dragon!
(screams)
And then she's
sending Warrior Einder
to attack the
fighter, Gao!
I cast my famous
Green Dragon Shield!
And with that he's used
the last Dragon Shield card
remaining in his hand.
But nothing can stop this girl's
next electrifying attack.
She hits Gao with
another Solar Panel Man!
I cast Dragonic Formation!
And I use Drum's
move ability.
He doesn't need
more shield cards
cause he's got
a shield in me.
Solar Kick.
(grunts)
The rest is up
to you, kid.
No problem!
It's not over yet.
‐I cast.
‐What's that?
The super spell
Hero Climax can be used
after a player defeats two or
more of an opponent's monsters.
Thanks to playing
this special card,
Paruko gains
two whole life points.
And it allows UFO Takosuke
to attack one more time.
UFO Battle Skill!
(groaning)
Galaxy Crash!
(screaming)
And he's down to
just one life point!
Meaning my victory is
as sure as my hair is pink!
I never thought
the day would come.
He might actually be out of the
running after the first round.
(groans)
This is bad.
I didn't travel all
this way for nothing.
You're back.
Yeah.
How's Gao doing
in the fight?
Even though victory
is all but assured,
our starlet's
hesitating.
Knowing his luck,
Gao might still draw
his Roaring Slash
Gargantua Punisher card.
That could
change things.
‐Hang on a sec.
‐Huh?
I won't let
you tell people
that my playing style
is just a matter of luck.
Explosive Dragon Fang
is a special deck
that was made just for me
by probably the greatest
deck builder ever.
That's why the card
I need shows up in my hand
just when I
need it the most.
Cool, thanks, bro.
♪
Knowing his track record,
he's probably gonna draw it.
♪
(roaring)
That's quite an
amazing impact card.
I really can't find the words
to describe what just happened.
It wasn't very professional,
but that's all I
could think to say
when I first saw Roaring
Slash Gargantua Punisher.
Understandable, but you
shouldn't let it get you down.
You're not alone.
Everyone there was
astonished by it, I'm sure.
You just happened to
have the microphone.
M'lady is right.
To me, it speaks as a
testament to your dedication
as a Buddyfight
announcer, Miss Nanana.
As you know, I was
fortunate enough
to be on the receiving end
of Gao's previous impact card.
Gargantua Punisher!
It was completely
unlike anything
I had ever
witnessed in my life.
I felt scared, while
at the same time,
feeling a real
sense of joy.
Even though I
lost the fight,
I'm very glad I was able
to personally experience
such an incredible move.
I will never forget it.
That's my dear
lady, Suzuha.
She's the pinnacle of
elegance even when defeated.
Well, I've done commentary
on the Gargantua Punisher.
I'm sure I can
handle it in a match.
Just remember,
there's a big difference
between watching
from the sidelines
and experiencing
it for yourself.
Huh?
Take it from me.
Experience is a treasure
greater than any other.
"Experience is a treasure
greater than any other."
So am I gonna win this
tie‐breaking game
as the final fighter
of Team Goddess
or am I gonna
use this moment
to become a
better announcer?
I guess it all comes
down to Gao's next draw
and charge and draw.
I'm leaving my future
in your hands, Mr. Mikado.
♪
Draw.
(grunts)
Charge and draw.
Okay.
It's time for
Final Phase!
‐I cast!
‐Impossible to neutralize.
Useless to defend against.
The incredible impact
card that delivers
five damage points
is about to be unleashed!
One dramatic move acts
as the beginning for one
and the end for the other.
In the blazing heat, the sun
finally reveals its true form.
Impact!
This attack threatens to the
change the world as you know it.
It's both shocking
and beautiful.
Don't blink or
you might miss it.
Roaring Slash...
Gargantua Punisher!
If this is the only way to
become a great announcer,
Paruko has no regrets!
(roaring)
♪
Game over.
Winner: Gao Mikado.
Alright!
It's all in the
deck, people!
‐Yes!
We're in the
groove, A‐Dog!
Now we're heading
to the semi‐finals.
Hmm!
You did it again.
Thanks, Gao.
(groaning)
That was rather
disappointing.
‐Huh?
‐Tako‐chu?
I'm sorry.
I‐‐I almost had him.
I tried.
I'm not referring
to your fight,
but to your commentary.
Sebastian here
could have done better.
I know you.
You should be able
to express Gao's impact
using much more lively
accurate descriptions.
I can only hope
that in the future
you'll use the things
you learned today,
and that you'll give Roaring
Slash Gargantua Punisher
the full airtime
it deserves.
Right, I'll
do my best!
Now, it's time for
the next two teams
in the first round of the
Gaen Cup to step forward.
But at the request
of both teams,
there's been a special
exception made.
All players will now be named
before their games begin.
First up, is Team
Three Brothers Konmae!
I'm Akaoni.
And I'm Aooni.
And this is my match,
I'm Kurooni.
And we three brothers are gonna
take this tournament by storm!
(crowd whispering)
It's not surprising
that the crowd's unsettled.
I mean, everyone knows
that two of the brothers
are criminal fighters who were
arrested by the Buddy Police.
Akaoni and Aooni have been
trying to change their ways,
so we gave them special
permission to participate.
We've always made an
effort to give offenders
second chances
when they're due.
Competing in this
tournament will help them
complete the transformation
of their characters.
It's in the very spirit
of Buddyfighting.
There's no other
game quite like this.
So please join me now,
and welcome these
fighters here today.
(indistinct whispering)
And their fierce opponents are
Team Darkness Masterminds.
Featuring Aibo student council
president Magoroku Shido
and well‐known cheat,
Davide Yamazaki.
Is it just me or is it weird
that they know each other?
And hey, where's
the third member?
Let's just say
we're keeping him on ice.
We plan on sweeping
the first two games,
so he's not needed yet.
What'd you say?
You think you're
any match for us?
Come over here
and say that!
I can see that your
pride's been hurt,
but we're superior
in every way.
Believe what he says for
the world we fight for
is none other than the
Darkness Dragon World!
(gasps)
What's wrong, Baku?
(breathing heavily)
There's no
doubt about it.
Team Darkness Mastermind's
third fighter's got to be him.
♪
You know I'll
never join you.
♪
Give it up, coach.
Cut your ties
with Disaster.
♪
The decks you build are too
supportive of their fighters.
Huh?
You're confused.
People should
not use decks.
Decks should
use people.
"Decks should
use people?"
♪
No way!
I won't agree to that.
♪
Hmm.
I guess the next time
we meet, we'll be enemies.
♪
It's time for...
Tasuku and Gao's...
‐Card of the day.
Today we're gonna
be talking about
Katana World's new impact card:
Super Lethal Formation.
How is it different from
Secret Sword Lethal Formation?
Well, when you set the
spell and pay one gauge,
all of the ninja cards that a
player has out on the field
get a boost of
1,000 power and defense.
So while you're laying
the trap for your opponent,
the card already starts
strengthening your ninja.
So, what do
you think, guys?
You think you could
open up one of these?
You'll never
know until you try!
♪
Next time the third match up of
the first round gets underway.
Team Sengoku Academy
versus Team Purgatory.
Plus, Rouga gets
really mad at Kyoya,
but you'll
never guess why!
Next episode,
"Attack of Team Purgatory!"
Join us for
a Buddyfight!