Do you have what it
takes to Buddyfight?
Choose your favorite world,
and use special cards
to summon its powerful
monsters into reality.
Challenge other fighters,
and Buddy call your toughest
ally to fight by your side.
Get ready to raise the flag.
I gotta hand it to ya.
You've put together
an awesome combo here.
But I'm confused why you need
to depend on that dark power.
To win, why else?
Is winning really
that important?
Of course it is.
Winning is everything.
Nothing else
matters to me at all.
(grunting)
You can't actually
believe that.
I call to the center
the Thunder Knight,
Bastard‐sword Dragon.
Did he say the
Bastard‐sword Dragon?
What's the matter, Kiri?
You're breaking
into a cold sweat.
What's your problem?
Come on!
You really want to know?
I got tired of losing
and tired of feeling
cheated all the time.
But you wouldn't know
about that, would you?
The Dark Core will make
you throw everything away!
(shouting)
♪
There are some
things more important
than winning and losing.
You should know that!
This will teach you
right from wrong!
(grunting)
♪
(footsteps)
Here it is, Kemura,
the Aibo Academy campus.
Wow, it's something, isn't it?
Come on, I'll introduce you
to the members
of the Seifukai.
Giving guided
tours now, Genma?
What, not happy to see me?
Wait, isn't that
Frog Monster,
the one who defeated
you over at Sengoku?
‐Hmm!
‐How rude!
Who are you calling
a monster, huh?
He may look and act
differently than we do,
but there's no need to be
throwing labels around!
You get me, weasel?
Huh, hey, who was that?
(chuckling)
(grunting and shouting)
(laughing)
That's it?
After hearing his voice,
I was expecting
someone much scarier.
To be honest,
he's kind of cute.
Hey, what are you thinking
showing up in your mini form?
You said to make
an impression.
Don't get smart.
Cute is not what
I was going for.
Now change back!
Ah!
Feast your trembling eyes
on my Death Ruler, Gallows.
Now, this is my real Buddy.
So, Genma, do you
dare to take us on?
What do you mean
"real Buddy"?
Whose Buddy did you use
with your Ancient World deck
in the ABC Cup?
Oh, that?
That was just to
throw you guys off.
And you fell for it too.
But this is my real deck...
Hmm?
...to defeat all
fools who cross me.
Dark Luminize, Black
Cloud of Endless Doom!
(slamming)
I fight for
Darkness Dragon World.
♪
I didn't think
that world existed.
Have you ever heard
of it, Kemura?
Mm‐mm.
(sighing)
(roaring)
Listen here, Shido,
it doesn't matter
what no‐good, dirty
trick you're up to.
You'll be thwarted
by the mighty power
of my Dragon Emperor,
Duel Sieger.
Mm, yada, yada, yada.
Blah, blah, yawn.
(gasping)
Death Ruler, Cremation,
eyes on Genma, and attack!
(shouting)
What's this?
Consumed in flames!
No, don't!
Ahh!
Next, the dark jester
Death Ruler, Burial.
Hm.
♪
(laughing)
(shouting)
My wit is sharp too.
Ah!
(gasping)
(grunting)
And, now, Death Ruler, Gallows.
(laughing)
Sh‐‐sh‐‐shall we dance?
(whooshing)
Great Gallows
under pressure!
Gen‐‐Genma!
As you can see, Death Rulers
are not to be taken lightly.
They can move around
the center monster
and attack the
fighter directly,
like a dangerous two‐step.
Ha‐cha!
What do you say?
You up for more?
Just getting started.
Oh, wait, I almost forgot.
Whenever Gallows inflicts
damage on an opponent,
I recover life points.
And once you factor in the
point for my buddy call,
the damage Sieger caused
earlier is cancelled.
I end up completely unharmed.
Your move.
I'm gonna draw.
And then I'm gonna
charge and draw!
Ahh!
Attack him, Sieger!
Sieger Tornado!
(whooshing)
(grunts)
Double attack!
(roaring)
End of move.
That's an amusing
sideshow you have,
but it's time for
your final curtain call.
Your move.
I draw.
Charge and draw!
I call Death Ruler,
Burial to the center!
♪
You only have three
life points left.
This match is over.
Now, go get him, Gallows!
(laughing)
With gloom and sorrow
and eternal darkness,
your hand's been dealt!
Cast Dragon Flame Cascade!
♪
(shouting)
Sh‐‐sh‐‐shame on you.
Did you see that?
Me do, Kem.
Dragon Flame Cascade
destroys all opponent monsters
with 2,000 or less
power or defense.
The unique skills of
these Death Rulers
caught me a little off‐guard,
but it looks like
their low defense
has done you in, Shido.
(laughing)
Hmm?
Time for final phase.
How can that be?
I cast Nightmare Despair!
(whooshing)
Leave him alone!
(roaring)
♪
Tell me, what did you do?
Change him back.
It's my not‐so‐secret weapon,
a specialty attack where
I add one critical point
to the opponent's
center monster
and, then, use it to attack
the opposing player for me.
You can't.
You wouldn't.
(gasping)
Face it, Genma,
your Duel Sieger
has become my puppet
of destruction!
♪
(shouting)
Game over.
Winner, Magoroku Shido.
Ooh, Darkness Dragon
World's impressive,
some might even
say beautiful.
Kemura, I need
to ask a favor.
I'd like you to
find Gao Mikado
and warn him about this
Darkness Dragon World.
Me do it, but...
I don't get it.
Why can't you just go
and tell him yourself?
Because there's
somewhere else I need to be.
I must return to the
mountains to train.
Hm?
Hey, aren't you a Four
Demon general from Sen Cad?
Yeah, it's Kemura, right?
Mmhmm.
Me must tell something
to Gao Mikado, Kem.
To Gao?
Huh?
Well, you know, we were
just hanging with him
at his place before
he had to take off.
But you could chill with
us until he gets back.
Hm?
(indistinct chattering)
Be real, kid.
Do you honestly think
Kiri's gonna show
himself after yesterday?
No, but I don't have
any choice, do I?
I don't know where he lives,
so my best chance
is to wait here.
(sighing)
Just for a second you can
see how I used to feel.
Give me a chance!
It's us who were
never really friends.
Don't go with him!
I will never go back to being
that weakling ever again.
Boy, that sounds like
it was pretty tough.
So, what is it you
need to tell Gao?
Uh, me need tell him about
Darkness Dragon World, Kem.
Whoa, are you saying you've
actually seen that world?
That's so boss.
What was it like?
Mmhmm, mmhmm.
Ooh, I've read about it.
It's relatively unknown
and its existence has only
recently been confirmed
which means there
aren't any cards yet.
And as it has no
official ties to Earth,
its monsters aren't even
supposed to be here.
They were here!
We saw them with
our own eyes!
Which fighter was
playing for it?
It was, uh, I don't know.
Don't look at me.
You know how I am with names.
Wait, he did wear kind of a
silly‐looking green uniform.
(gasping)
I'm sorry, President
Shido's very busy.
Besides, you know the rules.
No one gets to see him
without an appointment.
Now good day.
(yawning)
Hmm?
Kem‐Kem, is that you?
Ah?
Hey, long time no see.
So what brings you
all the way to Aibo?
Glad to see you,
you ill‐mannered mongrel!
♪
(sighing)
Sorry, I'm just
majorly spacing out.
♪
It's just all this
reminds me of stuff.
The deck that I want
to put together?
Why, that's easy, Baks.
It's called
Darkness Dragon World.
But why do you like that one?
Because it's a deck that
no one's ever built before.
I'll never forget the day
when he explained
to me what it was.
Hang on, is that
your cousin Retsu
that you're always
talking about?
Yeah, he's the
one who taught me
how to build my first deck.
He is one of the best.
Is that my new deck
you're holding?
You're smart when
you want to be.
♪
(clinking)
Oh.
I heard the one
you made Shido
totally rocked that Seifukai
leader to the core earlier.
That's what they're saying.
So, who should I
take on first?
(laughing)
What a fascinating planet.
This'll be fun,
don't you think?
You know it.
The world will never be
the same, Deathgaze.
(laughing)
We should just
go over to Gao's
and wait for him
to come home.
‐'Kay.
‐What a move!
He's proving himself
to be a great fighter!
Sounds like someone's on
stage having a Buddyfight.
I'm gonna go and take a look.
You guys coming?
Yeah, come on, let's go
check it out, too.
Hey, what?
‐Let go.
‐Kem, Kem.
(heavy breathing)
♪
What the what?
I wouldn't want to
mess with that dragon.
Buddy call to the center,
my Death Dragon,
Deathgaze Dragon.
Ah!
(grunting)
The Castle Store
manager is toast!
The guy using the
Darkness Dragon World deck
won the match with
surprising ease.
Two people are using it?
Who is that guy?
Game over.
Winner, Davide Yamazaki.
Wasn't me, it was
my Deathgaze Dragon.
He's the bomb.
I don't mean to brag‐‐oh,
wait, no, I totally do.
Something's up, bro.
Don't you think
it's kind of sketchy
that two people are using
Darkness Dragon World decks?
I mean, we didn't
even know for sure
it even existed until today.
Really, you want
to fight against me?
That's right.
Hmm.
Be careful.
What's wrong?
You're not gonna
back down, are ya?
Hey, you!
Ya gotta tell me, kid.
Where'd you get
that deck from, huh?
Hm.
Oh!
(gasping)
You should watch where
you're going next time.
Hey, are you hurt,
Mr. Manager?
I'm okay.
(chuckles)
Apologize for what you did!
Heh, or then what?
You'll refuse to
accept my challenge?
Then I'm sorry.
I'm really, really sorry.
(grunting)
How's that work for ya?
You ignoramus!
Kazane never
agreed to fight you,
and if I have
anything to say‐‐
Hey, hands off the sword!
I'll fight ya.
Kazane Fujimiya,
it's nice to meet you.
Uh, yeah, sure.
Actually, my real name
is Austine Fongspray.
Oh, that's an unusual name.
(laughing)
I'm just pulling your leg.
Well, it's nice to meet you,
whatever your name is.
Ditto, lady!
That is no way to behave.
The next battle is between
Dungeon World user
Kazane Fujimiya
and Davide Yamazaki,
user of the mysterious
Darkness Dragon World.
Charge and draw.
His Darkness Dragon
World deck is strong.
This is gonna be fun.
That impish rogue has a
mighty chip on his shoulder.
We need to teach him a
lesson he won't soon forget.
Hm, you could learn one too.
Remember, Blade, Buddyfights
are supposed to be fun.
Hm, I call Gummy Slime
to the center area
and Dragonblade Wielding
Sheila Vanna to the left.
♪
What's she doing, huh?
Most people don't call
more than one monster
during their first turn.
Okay, Sheila, do me proud
and attack the fighter.
(shouting)
End of move.
Hm, I get it now.
You brought out Gummy Slime
to increase Sheila's attack,
which was pretty
smart, actually.
I never pegged you to be
quite so aggressive though.
Well, I caught the end
of your last match,
so I know you're not
gonna be a pushover.
Your move.
(laughing)
She is feisty.
This is gonna be fun.
Huh?
The more units you bring out,
the happier it makes me and my
awesome Black Dragon deck...
...'cause it means there are
more monsters to wipe out!
I call to the center
Bloody Moon Dragon!
(growling)
You ready?
I buddy call to the right
Death Dragon,
Deathgaze Dragon!
Go attack Sheila!
(laughing)
That's it, show her
your amazing power!
♪
Ah!
Now here's a taste of
what your friend just had.
Spectral Strike!
Ah!
‐Ah!
‐What was that?
I don't know.
Kazane!
He's crazy.
‐What a match.
‐Are you all right?
Did he hurt you?
I'm okay.
Hey, Gummy, thought I
forgot about you, huh?
Gummy?
Crescent moon pass!
Not again!
This is harsh.
I've never seen
anything like it!
With each monster
he destroys,
he's somehow causing
direct damage to Kazane too.
My Dark Dragons
enjoy destroying
opponents' monsters so much
that their excitement
carries over a little bit
to take a bite
out of the fighter.
I like to call it...
...the Spectral Strike.
The Spectral Strike?
So the more units
you bring out,
the more life
points you will lose.
(laughing)
(grunting)
What a waste of time.
I told you Kiri
wouldn't show up, kid.
‐At least I tried.
‐So then what do we do now?
I don't know, we can't
just wait around forever.
Huh?
(indistinct chattering)
Looks like there's
a Buddyfight going on.
Looks like.
Swoop around again, Blade,
and attack the
fighter one more time!
Take that, scoundrel!
Raptor Blades!
(grunting)
Hey, look who it is.
Who, tell me, is it Kiri?
Is he here?
(gasping)
Davide Yamazaki.
You could say I'm Kiri's
one and only true friend.
What is he doing
here at Castle?
Ah.
And what kind of
flag is that?
♪
Kemura!
Hello, Kem.
What have I been
missing out on?
What a turn for Kazane!
Her flurry of timely attacks
have knocked her opponent's
life down to just one point!
But it's his turn now.
Let's see how he responds.
I'm impressed.
This young lady is strong.
Oh, really now?
Like I don't know.
As they say,
"The stronger the fighter,
the more enjoyable the battle."
That all depends.
Sometimes even a one‐sided
thrashing is just as fun.
This has sure been
one memorable match...
(laughing)
...but now it's
time to finish it!
(gasps)
Draw!
Hey, he just took that
card out of his pocket.
I call Bloody Moon Dragon
to the center area.
♪
Okay, Deathgaze.
It's feeding time!
Go and pluck that
overstuffed owl of hers!
Ah!
Dragon claw!
I'll rise again!
Spectral strike!
Ahh!
Come on, Bloody Moon,
I saved the rest for you.
Crescent moon pass!
Ahh!
You've served me well,
my fearsome friend,
but your work here is done.
I cast Devil Stigma!
(grunting)
(roaring)
That's devil sacrifice,
Devil Stigma.
It's tough destroying
my own monster,
but it does give me more
life points and gauge.
Now it's time to move
on to the next step.
Final phase!
I cast.
(grunting)
♪
Ah!
I don't understand!
For some reason, Davide has
just destroyed his own Buddy.
Hm, it's Slow Pain Fall.
(screaming)
Oh, man, that guy's hardcore.
(groaning)
♪
Game over.
Winner, Davide Yamazaki.
What happened?
What card was that?
Aw, that's so nice
of you to ask.
By destroying
one Black Dragon,
I get to deal four damage
points to my opponent.
The card's called
Slow Pain Fall.
Whoa, this world's
majorly powerful.
(sighing)
Huh?
♪
Uh...
Mm.
It's time for...
...Tasuku and Gao's...
...Card of the Day!
Today we're gonna
talk to you about
Darkness Dragon World's
very cool Death Dragon,
Deathgaze Dragon.
And its awesome
ability Spectral Strike
causes damage points
to the fighter
each time it destroys one
of an opponent's monsters.
Unlike Penetrate,
damage can be given
even if it's a
monster on the left
or right that's defeated.
It'd be wicked to have
one of those, hey, Tasuku?
So what do you think, guys?
You think you can
open up one of these?
You'll never know
until you try.
♪
Next episode, we're all
hanging out at Buddy Fest
when Davide turns up.
Quick to show off, as usual,
he reveals a crazy,
new technique.
Next episode, "Roaring Slash!
Gargantua Punisher!"
You'll want to
crash this party!