Do you have what it
takes to Buddyfight?
Choose your favorite world
and use special cards
to summon its powerful
monsters into reality.
Challenge other fighters
and Buddy Call
your toughest ally
to fight by your side.
Get ready to raise the flag!
Huh, Captain Answer?
I mean, Mr. Neginoyama.
Tasuku's gone to the mine?
Don't tell me he's planning to
take care of this on his own.
It seems that way.
Huh, Takihara, wait!
He's been through
enough, don't you think?
It's about time that
somebody did something.
♪
I told you, Kiri Hyoryu
doesn't exist anymore.
‐I'm the Grim Reaper.
‐So that's how it is?
Just remember, it didn't have
to go down like this, Kiri.
When a fighter loses a
battle to the Grim Reaper,
their bond with
their buddy is broken.
Think about it, Gao.
Are you really prepared
for that result?
Your call, kid.
Cracking the skies
and rumbling the ground!
Luminize the forceful
Tempest Thunder Knights!
Just like frozen water, my
power makes me tough to break.
Dark luminize
Unstoppable Ice Blizzard.
‐Time to raise the flag!
I fight for Dragon World.
♪
I'm with Legend World.
I activate Jackknife
Dragon's ability.
By paying two gauge,
he will evolve
into the Mighty
Jackknife Thunder Storm.
I wonder, who's he
gonna attack first?
It depends, if he goes
after the most irritating,
‐it'd have to be you.
‐Okay, Jack, go take out Shido!
‐What, why me?
‐Jackknife Battle Blade!
(shouting)
Not fair!
End of move.
Well, that's the
great Tasuku for you.
He realized I was the strongest
and posed the biggest
threat to him.
If you ask me, he
just attacked the one
‐who seemed easier to defeat.
‐Your move.
You're about to find out that
two can play at that game.
Draw, Charge and Draw.
I call Death Ruler,
Burial to the center,
and the left,
Death Ruler, Cremation!
And I Buddy Call Death Ruler,
Gallows to the right!
Calling on me already, Shido?
Buddies can be called
at any time, Gallows.
Fly, Death Rulers,
an all‐out attack!
‐Terrible Cremation!
‐From darkness and beyond!
Shall we dance?
♪
End of move.
Doubt you could
cause five damage.
‐Clearly I'm much better.
‐Sorry, what's that?
‐I wasn't really watching.
‐No one pays attention to me!
You know, it just
doesn't feel right
to be playing two against one.
‐Huh?
‐You're kidding?
You should see the
look on your faces!
I'm only kidding, numbskulls,
two on one is the best!
Any advantage we can get, right,
even if it means joining
forces with lame‐o here.
Are you planning to attack?
Someone's in a hurry to lose.
I call to the left
Black Dragon, Cold Blade.
And I Buddy Call to the right,
Death Dragon, Deathgaze Dragon!
Then I'll also equip
Evil Death Scythe,
but first, I'm going
to enjoy exterminating
that cocky buddy lizard
of yours, Jackknife Dragon.
Rise, Deathgaze, you're on.
I cast Blue Dragon Shield!
Ha, Jack's really that
precious to you, is he?
In that case, I'm going
to enjoy crushing him
in a link attack with
me and Black Dragon.
♪
I cast Green Dragon Shield!
‐That's just luck.
‐What's he doing now?
Why doesn't he just
attack Tasuku directly?
He did force Shido to use
two counterspell cards.
So next time he can't
deflect any damage.
‐Your move.
‐I draw.
Charge and Draw.
I hope he isn't going
to attack me again!
It's time, Jack, I'm gonna
use some of my life.
‐You sure?
‐I'll use two life points,
and activate Jackknife
Thunder Storm's ability
to destroy one monster.
Show him who's boss, Jack!
Thunder Raid!
Ahhh!
Impressive.
I guess you realized
I'm the real threat.
Just don't try to pull anything.
I know that you like to
cheat, but I won't let you.
I don't know what
you're talking about.
Besides, I've done my homework.
Let's see, you have
a special power
that's different from ours,
and your only
friends are dragons.
You joined the Buddy
Police to help people
and lock up bad guys who
go against your values,
‐but it's none of your business.
‐Is that right?
Where has all your dumb
do‐gooding gotten you anyway?
I mean, you're here all
alone, and the Buddy Police
don't even care
what happens to you.
If you ask me, it looks like
you've chosen the wrong path
and it's time to pick a new one.
‐Mine is the path of justice.
‐For now.
I pay one gauge and evolve Jack
into Jackknife Dispersal!
(growling)
This is new.
Now I'll pay one more
gauge and evolve him
‐into Jackknife Aggressor.
‐Ahh!
If he keeps evolving like this,
we won't stand a
chance against him.
Don't worry, Davide
can handle this.
Successive cast,
Dragonic Charge!
Dragonic Grimoire!
(chuckling)
Dragonic Grimoire
is a spell card
that lets you discard all
the cards in your hand
and draw three new cards.
Let's see what he gets.
♪
What's going on,
you okay over there?
I can't believe it's real,
I thought this special
Rare Card was just
some crazy urban legend,
but if I use it, everything
will change forever.
Will he take the bait?
What am I worried about?
I promised myself I'd become
an adult as soon as I could,
and if this is the only way
I can gain more power, then‐‐
Places to go, people to meet.
Jack, you're my buddy,
my best friend,
and the only real family I have,
but I have to do
this, so I will.
I will face solitude
without fear or regret,
and I will wield
the blade of justice.
‐I equip!
‐No, wait!
If you use that card
you know what'll happen!
I'm sorry, forgive me.
Tasuku!
Just one question remains,
will he be able
to master that card?
By combining the power of
dragons and the power of humans,
a golden era is created!
A human and a dragon unite!
Behold Jackknife Gold Ritter!
Hold on, did he just
equip a dragon?
Looks like he changed his
own buddy into an item.
Definitely the
greatest achievement
of the Jackknife Deck.
Although Gold Ritter is an
item, its attack and power
count the same as a
size three monster does.
So from now on, I'm
the one in control.
His buddy no longer has
any free will of its own.
It's become the Buddy Cop's
weapon and nothing more.
(screaming)
♪
Penetrate!
I inflict five damage!
End of move.
I hope you have an
answer for that!
I have just the thing.
I cast Guillotine Cutter!
What happened, it didn't
even make a dent!
It's no use, Gold Ritter is
a card that can't be destroyed
and can't be returned
to the hand.
Says you, he won't last with
his center wide open, I hope.
Gold Ritter's power and
defense are both 10,000.
It is possible to break through
it, but if you can't launch
an attack of that
amount or more,
than you won't cause any damage.
A fighter with defense?
I've never even heard
of such a thing!
I call to the center
Death Ruler, Cremation!
♪
Now, Death Rulers, do
a triple link attack!
I cast Green Dragon Shield!
You haven't seen the last of us!
‐End of move.
‐Talk about a useless turn.
‐Your move.
‐Those shield cards of his
have got to run out
sooner or later.
I call Deathgaze to the right.
Tails up, we're gonna do
a triple link attack too.
Come on, follow me!
♪
Take this!
‐End of move.
‐I knew it would work,
but why'd we only take
two damage off of him?
That's because Gold Ritter
will only receive two damage
when it's hit with
a link attack.
‐In that case, we're doomed!
‐It's my turn next,
and I'm just getting started.
Should I have seen this coming?
How did you end up like this?
I wish I could've stopped
you before it got this bad.
Can't you see that what you're
doing right now is wrong?
How can having the strength
I've always dreamed of be wrong?
It's time for you to wake up!
‐End of move.
‐Nice.
I woke up when I became
the Grim Reaper.
You wouldn't get it.
I equip Rune Staff,
and increase my gauge by one.
Did you ever hear
the story about the boy
who was obsessed with the sun?
The thing is, he couldn't
get too close to it
or the heat of the sun
would burn everything up,
including him.
So the boy had to
distance himself from it.
He was forced to go
away and discover
the power to survive on his own.
He found it in ice, the
complete opposite of the sun.
Are you talking about the
Dark Core Deck Case, come on!
Being alone is what
makes people strong.
Friends are unnecessary.
I call to the center position
Corpse Swallower, Hraesvelgr.
Attack the fighter!
♪
End of move.
I don't know if it's my fault or
not that you ended up like this,
Kiri, but I've always
tried to have your back.
Yeah.
You may not know it, but,
nothing is ever gonna change
the fact that you're my friend!
Drop the act, I have
no real friends.
Draw!
Charge and Draw!
I call to the left area Thunder
Knights, Broadsword Dragon!
Then it's time to Buddy Call!
(grunting)
I call Drum to the right.
Broad and Drum, do a
link attack on Hraesvelgr!
‐All right!
♪
Penetrate!
‐Remember, you're my‐‐
‐Don't say it.
I cast Shield of Achilles!
You're my friend!
‐End of move.
‐That's cool!
After everything, he still
wants to chill with ya.
Why can't you understand that
I don't need you anymore?
Your move.
Others only hold me back.
Now, Rune Staff
increases my gauge by one.
I set the spells Gleipnir,
and Great Spell, Fimbulwinter.
Gleipnir's soul contains
Demon Wolf, Fenrir.
And remember what happens
when Fimbulwinter's soul
‐is reduced to zero?
‐Great Spell, Ragnarok
will come and destroy
all cards on the field.
But it has a two‐card soul, so
we still have two more turns.
Oh, I don't know about that.
I call to the center
Loki the Ehrgeiz.
Now you're in trouble.
I'm sure you don't know
this, but when called,
Loki has a cool ability
that can destroy every card
in the soul of any
one card in the field.
Whoa, that's an awesome ability.
‐You mean‐‐
‐You guessed it.
I destroy all the
cards in the soul
of set spell Great
Spell, Fimbulwinter!
Leave it to me.
This is too easy.
‐Okay.
‐When there's a Fimbulwinter
in the field and
the soul is at zero,
Great Spell, Ragnarok
can be activated.
Are you ready, this is
gonna be a tough one.
I cast Great Spell, Ragnarok!
With its effects,
all cards on the field
and in the players' hands
are destroyed and discarded.
Now I cast Dragon Barrier!
Your buddy is that
precious to you?
No matter, I'll destroy
everything else.
(ice shattering)
And now I call Demon
Wolf, Fenrir for free.
It normally would
cost me five gauge.
I'm hungry!
The cards in my hand
were destroyed too.
And since they were discarded
I'm able to Buddy Call again.
So I call to the right
Ice Blade, Joker.
Freeze!
This is great, I'm going
to take Gao Mikado's buddy.
Where is my prey?
Let's go, put me
in the center, kid.
No way, I'm not losing you!
Come and get me, Kiri!
Ice Blade, Joker, cut
the fighter down to size!
Ice Blades come cold and fast!
Now, Fenrir, you can devour him.
(growling)
Gao!
(screaming)
End of move.
(panting)
Tell me, you really
think you're all alone?
Of course I am, and
it's making me stronger.
I'll never leave you alone.
Might as well give up,
'cause you're stuck with me.
I attack Shido's Cremation
with my Gold Ritter!
‐Not the penetrate!
‐You're done!
I'm not worthy.
‐End of move.
‐I guess the only way
to fight Gold Ritter is
through link attack, huh?
Don't hold anything back!
I cast Green Dragon Shield!
End of move.
Heads up, guys,
it's up to us now.
You are going down!
‐End of move.
‐Davide does have six life left,
but unless he can beat
Tasuku's Gold Ritter,
there's no way he
can win this thing.
I have an idea.
If you're thinking of
cheating, think again.
You're a quick one, aren't ya?
I'm beginning to think
you're not even human.
Are you a dragon?
Or maybe even a unicorn?
Either way, I'll have to start
putting some effort into this.
To the center, Cold Blade!
Now two Cold Blades
attack the fighter!
I cast Blue Dragon Shield!
I kinda had a feeling
you'd do that.
I cast, using
Death Grip I destroy
the Cold Blade in the center.
And now I'm gonna do a link
attack with Deathgaze!
Ahh!
You just destroyed
your own monster
so you could open up the center?
It's no different from
what you did to Jack,
and there's more
where that come from.
I cast Devil Stigma!
(shouting)
You just destroyed another
one of your monsters
to increase your gauge?
It's obvious, he's planning
on doing his move!
And now, final phase, I cast.
(groaning)
Say hello to Slow Pain Fall.
♪
Looks like lights
out for Tasuku.
He has only three
life points remaining,
and Slow Pain Fall
causes four damage.
Even Gold Ritter can
be hit by an ability.
I cast my White Dragon Shield!
‐End of move.
‐An excellent play.
That spell reduces all
damage by two points.
Davide fails once again, pity.
I cast Dragonic Heal.
Hey, Buddy Cop, let me
tell you something.
‐I'm listening.
‐You're all alone,
without help from
any other monsters.
You've even manipulated
your buddy.
So who do you have
left to fight for?
I've always fought for justice!
Yeah, but for who's
justice, your own?
I've heard enough!
♪
I don't have to
explain myself to you.
I'm not like Gao, I'm
not here to save you.
I'm here to defeat
you once and for all!
Time for final phase!
I cast, Impact!
Dragonic Punisher!
(screaming)
♪
Game over, winner,
Tasuku Ryuenji.
Who's my next opponent?
Bravo, that was wonderful.
Very impressive, but tell me,
you're a smart guy,
you must have noticed
that I slipped that
card into your deck.
I only used it in
the name of justice!
Yes, that's right,
and fighting for justice
requires massive power and
a buddy to replace your Jack.
I'd be happy to give
you both of those things,
as a friend.
I'd like you to meet
my buddy, Azi Dahaka.
Now, why don't we
begin our fight?
You think you can get through
the ice that protects me?
But not even my own
buddy can get close.
You're the one
who should give up.
Oh yeah, then tell me,
what're we doing right now?
We're Buddyfighting, obviously.
‐You're missing the point!
‐Huh?
Don't you realize, Kiri,
that you can only Buddyfight
when you have an opponent?
You've never been alone,
not now, not ever!
Think about it, Kiri.
Buddyfighting is the most fun
we've ever had, and right now
we're having probably
the best Buddyfight ever!
The best Buddyfight, against me?
Here he goes.
Eclipsing the
darkness with flames
and brightening the
hearts of the mistreated.
(gasping)
The Mighty Sun Fighter is here.
No, stop it, I can't
play the Sun Fighter.
‐Sure you can, let's go.
‐Never!
You're too good, I
could never be like you.
Of course not.
Why would you wanna be?
You're you, and I think
that's pretty cool, man!
Be proud of who you are, you
can only find out how strong
you are when you
have an opponent.
And Drum and I will be
your opponents anytime!
Yeah, you don't need
to wear a crazy costume
‐to party with us, you know.
‐Here we go!
I call to the left Thunder
Knights, Dragoarcher!
With his ability
I draw one card.
Go on, link attack Fenrir!
‐You got it!
‐So that's why,
he protected Drum to
use him in his attack.
But wait, if Fenrir is defeated
then both of our center
positions will be open.
‐Penetrate!
‐Ahhh!
‐No, stop!
‐Come on, you gotta dig deep!
It's time to find the you
that you really wanna become.
Take off that mask
and I promise,
you'll get way
stronger, I know it!
Really?
Time for final phase!
I cast!
You'll see, we're gonna have a
ton more Buddyfights together,
and with each match, we'll keep
getting better and better!
You can count on it,
you'll always have me
and your buddy
right there with you.
Impact!
♪
Roaring Slash!
Gargantua Punisher!
(screaming)
(rumbling)
♪
It's so hot, all this
time I've been freezing.
What just happened to me?
This heat definitely
does not work for me.
I better slip away and cool down
or I'll end up a
puddle on the ground.
Anyone, anyone?
I'm sorry, man.
I wish I could've been there
for you when you needed my help.
Hm, don't be sorry, I think
what I really needed
was for you to beat me and
to remind me of who I am.
Without you, there's no way
I would've realized that.
Good to hear.
Thanks, Gao.
Hey, Joker, where are
the buddies and cards
that Kiri took from
the fighters he beat?
They're all back at the mine.
He said something about
using them for experiments.
‐That is not gonna happen.
‐Yeah.
‐I'll help you if you like.
‐Huh?
Is it me or are you
a little different?
I know, it's freaky, like my
mind was being controlled by
someone else, a giant maniacal
puppet master jerking me around
‐on an invisible strings‐‐
‐I'm sorry I asked.
♪
‐What went down?
‐Tasuku!
How could this have happened?
Which one of you could've
done this to him?
(groaning)
‐It's time for‐‐
‐Tasuku and Gao's‐‐
Card of the Day!
Today we're gonna be talking
a little about Jack's
ultimate evolution,
Jackknife Gold Ritter.
He turns into an item card
and gives the fighter
‐some wicked defense!
‐It's true,
and if the opponent can't
beat his 10,000 defense,
he won't receive any damage.
That's not all, even
if a fighter is hit with
a link attack, the damage
becomes two points.
It sounds totally unbeatable!
So what do you think, guys?
You think you can
open up one of these?
(together)
You'll never know until you try!
♪
Next time, Disaster figures out
a way to control Buddy Monsters,
and all the ones the Grim
Reaper took have been turned
into Elf Kabala's
puppets, even Tsukikage!
Next episode, Luminize,
Explosive Dragon Fang!
Join us for a Buddyfight!