♪
Get ready for a
cool new card game
that connects to
a parallel universe.
Special cards
act as portals,
bringing
monsters to Earth
to become
buddies with humans.
And through
friendship and courage,
help them take on
fight challenges.
It's called
Buddyfight.
♪
My son,
the day shall come
when you will
take my place
and lead the
Armordragon Army
of the Drum clan.
You have gained
much knowledge
that will serve you well.
(snicker)
But you still have
much to learn.
I'm sending you away
from our dragon world
to the alien planet
called Earth,
where it is my hope
that you will continue
on your path of knowledge.
As you wish, Father.
I'll become buddies
with the great‐‐
no, a perfect human,
who will
push me to become
the most awesome
dragon ever.
You buffoon!
Father?
If you truly wish to
become worthy of my crown,
you had better
learn to overcome
your stubborn attitude.
(crashing)
Actually, I think that's
one of my best qualities.
Do you?
Just keep one
important thing in mind.
The human you
eventually choose
to become buddies with
should by no
means be flawless.
♪
How shall I put this?
It should be someone
who's unconventional.
Unconventional‐‐
okay, Father.
♪
(distant siren blaring)
The fugitive
fighter was last seen
in the city center.
Suspect is currently fleeing
to the top of Sky Tower.
(siren blaring)
Let's go to work, Jack.
♪
(explosion)
Rahhhr!
Down here!
♪
Buddy skill on.
(siren blaring)
♪
Buddy police barrier.
Huh?
As I see it, you're
looking at only two options,
give yourself up
or else.
Accept my
buddyfight challenge.
Bring it on, punk.
Illuminize!
They never come
quietly, do they?
Fine by me.
Let's get to work.
♪
I'm live at Sky Tower
as buddyfighter
and boy wonder,
Buddy cop Tasuku Ryuenji
and Jackknife Dragon
prepare to take down
an escaped fugitive.
As some of
you probably know,
the child prodigy, Tasuku,
has never lost a buddyfight
to a criminal fighter.
Stay with us as
the action unfolds.
Assemble, dragon army!
Dragonic Force Luminize!
Raise the flag!
Arrgh!
Gao, Roars!
Tasuku's buddyfight
with the fugitive
is moving on
to the third turn.
Where are the files
I asked for?
Our man's running
blind out there.
The fugitive's fight history
is fully downloaded, sir.
It should be on
your screen now.
Tasuku, this is the
buddy card office.
It looks like
your opponent's
using a defensive
combo deck,
which could mean trouble
if you don't act fast.
10‐4.
Attack, Jackknife Dragon!
Get him!
Arrgh!
Urgh!
Where do you think
you're going?
(crashing)
Remember it well,
this is the
blade of justice
that terminates evil.
Unleash!
♪
Argh!
Impact card!
♪
Gargantua!
Punisher!
Aaahh!
(crashing)
♪
Whoa!
That Tasuku Ryuenji's
totally awesome!
Huh?
(murmuring)
♪
Oh, man, I wish I could
draw a buddy rare card
and become buddies
with a cool monster
like Jackknife Dragon.
Did he say
Jackknife Dragon?
That Tasuku's one cool
hombre, hey, Gao?
Yeah, you
think I could ever
buddyfight like that?
I don't see why not.
And I bet I could rock
Gargantua Punisher, too.
You know it!
Who am I kiddin'?
I'll never be able
to draw a buddy rare.
You got to be more positive.
You think I was just
made manager of this place?
If you really
want something,
you got to go
out and take it.
Like $100 store credit?
(laughing)
I don't have the
heart to tell him.
Everyone knows
Tasuku Ryuenji's
the only one
on the planet
who's got the majorly rare
Gargantua Punisher card.
Maybe he just started
buddyfighting.
(cell phone ringing)
Oh, heya, Mom.
Hey, yourself, why are
you avoiding practice?
I'm not avoiding
anything, I swear.
I was just taking
the scenic route home.
Stop sassing me
and get your butt
back here right now!
Ooh.
Catch you later.
(heavy breathing)
Ha ha!
♪
Listen up, twerp,
I'll ask you for
the last time,
do you have buddyfight
rare card or not?
I‐I told you,
I don't buddyfight.
Then I'm gonna
have to charge you
for wasting our time.
I don't think
that's gonna happen.
Arrgh!
Who do you think you are,
some kind of hero
or something?
Oh, I'm no hero.
I prefer to go by the title
Mighty Sun Fighter.
Ha ha ha,
you're hilarious.
That's got to be the
craziest thing I ever heard.
Alright, can't say
I didn't warn you.
Kid's got guts,
I'll give him that.
Teach him a lesson.
(evil laughter)
Ah!
Hey!
Aah!
(gasps)
♪
Stop playing around
and take him out!
(heavy breathing)
Oh, you are gonna
pay for that.
Right now!
♪
What's he doing,
he's dodging
every single attack.
It looks like
he's running away,
but he's actually
turning great defense
into incredible offense.
Aah!
Argh!
Now I'm angry!
Think you're pretty cool,
hey, tough guy?
Hmm?
Fifty of my main crew
are on their way
to back me up here.
F‐fifty?
You'll need a
lot more than fifty.
Ah!
Clips in the
darkness with flames
and brightening the hearts
of the mistreated.
I think this weirdo's
lost his marbles.
The Mighty
Sun Fighter is here!
Ever since I
was a little boy
I've had this dream
of fighting 100 guys.
So please,
call another 50.
Bring it on!
Uh.
Ah!
This is gonna get ugly.
♪
Uh, are you sure
you want to do this?
Don't worry, the Sun
Fighter will protect you.
Did he say Sun Fighter?
Well, what are
you waiting for?
Text your friends.
In the name of injustice,
the Mighty Sun Fighter
will take down
your whole entourage.
Time to claim your victory.
Attack!
(cell phone ringing)
What is it now, hello?
Why are you
keeping me waiting?
It's the funniest thing.
You see, I was running home
when I saw this kid‐‐
Don't lie to me!
Get home right now!
Oh.
We're gonna
have to reschedule
our little showdown
till tomo‐‐
Not a chance.
Let's get him!
Aaah!
(punching)
Ah.
‐Time to go!
‐He's getting away!
Uh, you've got
to be kidding me.
Ah, Mighty Sun
Fighter my butt!
I was hoping
to see a fight.
What a waste of time.
How can I ever repay you
for saving me
from those bullies?
Don't sweat it, man.
Catch you later.
Well, thank you
very much.
Hmm.
I'm home!
♪
You've been at it again,
haven't you, Gao?
Uh, at what again?
What are you talking about?
I warned you
that if you continue
getting into brawls,
there'll be
no more Sun Fighter.
Oh, oh, no!
Your punishment
for disobeying my wishes
will be 50 pushups
and extra training.
Come on, Mom!
Call me sensei.
Now, go change
into your uniform.
I was kinda hoping I
could get a snack first.
You can eat as
much as you like
after we've
finished our practice.
Oh, it sounds like they've
started Gao's training.
Here you go, Daddy.
Why thank you, Hanako.
Did Gao get in trouble
for becoming the Sun Fighter
and tackling a bunch
of bullies again?
Ugh.
Sure sounds like it.
Yeee!
Must have been so cool.
I bet he was all shiny
and heroic and stuff.
One thing's for sure,
you really do love
your big brother, don't you?
Yeah, 'cause the Sun
Fighter's totally sweet.
(snickering)
Now eat up
before it gets cold.
Hargh, easy, Mom.
Arrgh!
♪
I don't get how being
flipped on my butt
for three hours
counts as extra training.
Ugh, all 'cause I helped
out that little kid.
Good morning, Gao.
Huh?
Kuguro and Baku.
Hey, what's up?
Not much, I was
just asking Baku here
that if he could
chose buddy at all,
which world would
he chose from?
That's a good question.
Baku said he's never even
thought about it before
since, you know, he's
a deck builder and all.
Yeah, well, I'm sure
there's a lot of things
he hasn't thought about.
Yeah, right, look who's
talking, Mr. Sun Fighter.
(growling)
So, what about you, Gao?
The Dragon World?
The Magic Worlds?
Or the Danger Worlds?
Not an easy choice, huh?
Hmm, let me think.
My monster'd have
to have a big weapon.
Something he'd use
to crush anything
standing in our way.
So the world I'd pick for
such a choice monster is,
well, I don't know,
that's a tough one.
But as long as
he's mega strong,
it doesn't really matter.
How about a dragon knight?
Hmm, was that
a dragon knight?
Not sure about that,
but the dragon
Jackknife's pretty cool.
I never pegged you
for a dragon.
(snickering)
Ah, no way,
no way, no way!
I can't become
buddies with a guy
who runs away
from his fights.
Oh, yeah, dragons
are the only way to go,
trust me.
You like dragons, huh?
Huh, Noboru?
They're okay, but dragon knights
are way cooler.
Dragons are nothing
without their masters.
What is a dragon knight?
Take a look.
They're humans
that ride on dragons
and bravely fight
along side them.
Dragons are just
dim‐witted monsters
that couldn't even
find their own tails
without being ordered
to by a dragon knight.
Kind of lame, really.
Aaah, dragons
are dim‐witted?
Can't find
their own tails?
dragon knights
are weaklings!
All they do is
bark out orders
as if we don't
know what to do!
Listen up, kid.
Why don't you tell
your drooly friend there
why dragons are far
superior to dragon knights?
Yeah, maybe Noboru's right.
What is wrong with you?
Aaagh!
(splashing)
Dragons are the most
extraordinary creatures ever.
I'll have to show them.
Hurry, or we'll be late.
Leave him behind.
Come on, just hang on
a sec, would you, guys?
Gah!
Morning, class.
Today I have something
very exciting planned.
We're going to write essays
using a buddyfight
card pack.
I'd like you to
create short stories
using the monsters
you find inside
and make one of them
your main character.
Yeah, I got a
double rare card!
Ha, I can't believe it!
Check it out, a
Dragon Knight Maximillian.
Uh, maybe I've got one too.
A Systemic Dagger Dragon.
Okay.
Next one is...
ah, a Lotale
Shield Dragon!
(chewing)
And a Thousand
Rapier Dragon!
Man, all of
these monster cards
are so totally cool!
Ha, none of them are rare
though, are they, pal?
It doesn't matter.
Picking a double rare card
is beyond you anyways.
I mean, it takes
a lot of skill.
And now for the last card.
♪
‐Ah!
‐Oh!
What's happening?
Hey, wait,
that's my card!
Buddy monster reaction
is confirmed, sir.
In the 700 block of
West Tokyo district,
on the grounds of
Aibo School Academy.
It looks like
the monster is
Armor Dragon,
Drum Bunker Dragon.
Huh?
Are you quite
sure about that?
Yes.
‐(beeping)
‐Huh?
♪
Come back!
(oohing and aahing)
♪
All of a sudden now
you have nothing to say?
Ah?
♪
Yes, it's a dragon!
You've got to be joking.
♪
What are you
trying to pull, kid?
Just a handshake.
You are gonna be
my buddy, aren't you?
Hah, not if
I can help it.
Huh?
But you came
out of my card.
Doesn't that mean you
have to be my buddy?
You think dragon knights
are better than
dragons, do ya?
Or maybe I misheard you.
Well, I, uh, you know.
I'm waiting.
♪
Why do you listen
to that insolent
little friend of yours?
How dare he call me
a dim‐witted monster?
‐Well, Noboro?
‐You lucked out.
How does a guy like you
draw a buddy rare monster?
I just can't believe it.
It's so unfair.
Come on, don't be that way.
Huh?
I may not be the smartest,
or know everything
that you do,
but luck or no luck,
the trick
is to keep trying
and go after what
you really want.
Hmm.
Right?
Hey, don't you look at me.
I'm still ticked
'cause you believed
that whining
sore loser over there.
You want to buddy with me?
You better
show some respect.
Huh?
(loud flapping)
It's Jackknife Dragon.
‐Ha!
‐Whoa!
Sorry to just
drop in on you.
‐Huh?
♪
But actually, I'm here
on official business.
Do you know
who I am?
Tasuku Ryuenji!
(excited murmuring)
Tasuku and Jack from
the Buddy Police are here!
Look, there's Jack!
Well, I guess in the future
I should have you come
in mini form, huh?
You're right,
but I'd refuse.
Tasuku Ryuenji, the boy
wonder from the Buddy Police!
Why's he here
at our school?
Listen in and find out!
You're live with
school reporter extraordinaire,
Paruko Nanana, and her
faithful buddy sidekick
the one and only Hero World
Martian UFO, Takosuke!
Come on out, Takosuke!
♪
Tako‐chuuu!
Let's go!
♪
You're on active duty
or just come to see me?
To be honest, I came
here to deliver this
Core Deck Case to Gao.
Here, this
belongs to you now.
It can be transformed
into a core gadget,
which will allow you
to illuminize your deck.
Go on, take it.
Illuminize?
Any human who becomes
buddies with a monster
is given a Core Deck Case
from the buddy card office.
Didn't you know that?
And yes, of course,
I have one too.
♪
Gee, thanks.
This also makes you
an official buddyfighter.
Huh?
You're now able to go out
and buddyfight with monsters
at any time and any place
that you want.
Buddyfight with monsters?
Well, bye.
No, hang on,
where are you going?
What if I challenged
you to a fight
to help train me?
♪
Sorry, did I hear
you correctly?
You'd like to
buddyfight challenge me
and Jack from
the Buddy Police?
Yeah, well, you know,
if you're up for it?
(murmuring)
What a total dweeb.
It's too soon to be
challenging Master Tasuku
of the Buddy Police,
don't you think?
It's a no‐brainer that you
will be completely destroyed!
Use your head, kid,
it's common sense, right?
Forgive me if I don't
listen to common sense
coming from a girl
in a UFO.
Common sense?
It should be someone
who's unconventional.
Hmm.
But it's Jackknife Dragon.
Uh, whatever.
I have to try.
I must know my potential.
Hey you, little human?
From this moment on,
you and I will be buddies.
Did you say buddies?
Yes!
I am none other
than the son
of the honorable
Drum Bunker Dragon,
Fang Slade Terrestrial,
the Thirteenth.
How about I just
call you Drum?
Yeah, well
how about you don't!
Heh, whatevs,
I'm the leader.
The name's Gao,
Gao Mikado.
♪
You can still take
back your challenge
if you want to.
I don't want
to take it back.
I don't know why, but
I know I have to do this.
♪
That's why I'd
like to challenge you
to a buddyfight
right here and now.
♪
Hello there,
I'm Paruko Nanana,
your guide to the
buddyfight world.
Every episode
will introduce you
to some buddyfight
fun facts
and some super
cool techniques
that you can use at home.
Today we focused on
our own world, Earth.
As you saw, Gao's
buddy card got connected
to the Dragon World
and he met Drum.
That's 'cause buddy
cards are like portals
for monsters
from other worlds
to come hang out on Earth.
It's totally epic,
don't you think?
What do you think, guys,
can you open
a buddy rare card?
♪
On the next Buddyfight,
it's Tasuku versus Gao.
And although Gao's
a total newbie,
he holds his own.
Wait, why are
you calling me
to the right area?
They'll crush us with
Gargantua Punisher.
Gao versus Tasuku,
next time on Buddyfight.