Do you have what it
takes to Buddyfight?
Choose your favorite world
and use special cards
to summon its powerful
monsters into reality.
Challenge other fighters and
Buddy Call your toughest ally
to fight by your side.
Get ready to raise the flag.
Don't ever call or try to visit.
If I so much as see
your pathetic face
within 20 feet of me,
I'll take more
than your memories.
Wait, you said
you were my friend!
Was that just a lie?
I don't understand,
I did everything you asked!
How can you do this to me?
After all this time,
am I worth nothing to you?
Nice knowing you,
my friend.
♪
(explosion)
'Kay, according to Jin,
there's a research facility
somewhere inside the mine.
It should provide us
with some answers.
Are you ready?
Hmm.
I can't understand what
took the Buddy Police
so long to find this place.
Talk about late to the party.
Come on, they might
need our help.
Where are you going?
Wait for me!
Don't move!
We're the Buddy Police!
Hey, Miss Stella!
You're as beautiful as always.
Oh, you look nice, too.
Why are you sitting down
here all alone in the dark?
‐Huh?
‐Did I give you the impression
that I was all alone?
What's this?
Just a little meeting
between monsters.
I guess you could say
we're on official business.
Mr. Neginoyama.
I'm detecting that something is
quickly approaching the earth!
I sense it's a dark being
who was banished long ago.
There's one of us
here from each world.
We're kind of working
together to keep things chill.
Yeah‐huh, we're gonna
save Earth's butt.
But‐‐but, why are
there two Asmodais?
I'm reppin' Magic World,
and my handsome
friend here is...
Armorknight Asmodai,
a homie from Danger World.
We chose him because
he's not like the other
ill‐mannered rubes
from Danger World
who can barely string
two words together.
Oh, forgive me.
I am Bladewing Phoenix
of Dungeon World.
And I'm Kashinkoji
from Katana World.
‐(roaring)
‐Huh?
Oh, yeah, this is
Silver Dragon, Adelaide,
from Ancient World.
And, last but not least...
♪
Immortal Sword, Durandal,
from Legend World, of course.
Look at that!
There really are representatives
here from every world.
Hey, let's not
forget Hero World.
(coughing)
Why, I don't know what
you're talking about.
Huh?
What's happening?
Oh, an interdimensional portal
has been acting up a bit.
I'm really starting to
feel like something creepy
wants to get in through here.
I don't understand,
what makes you think
this being is a threat?
You all use portals.
Indeed, but each of us
was brought to your planet
through Buddy Cards.
This contraption is
something quite different.
I hear what you're saying.
I'll go and check
out the situation.
It could be dangerous.
Well, somebody has
to do it, right?
That thing is the reason
you've all gathered here,
if I'm not mistaken.
It is.
Allow me to go with you.
I will defend you.
Promise me you'll be careful.
This could help us uncover
Kyoya Gaen's mysterious plan.
Freeze, Buddy Police!
Ooh, I always
wanted to say that.
‐Kiri?
‐I'm responsible.
I should be the one
to take the risk.
I just hope wherever
we're going is not too hot!
Good luck, Kiri.
Are you sure that was
the right thing to do?
I mean, you're the one
who's always going on
about justice.
Maybe someday you'll understand.
Huh?
(commotion)
What's going on?
Just leave it to
me, big brother.
(chuckling)
That's it, one at a time.
No pushing now.
Don't worry, there
are plenty left.
Former Vice President Sofia?
I didn't think she
even knew how to smile.
Hmm?
Today, and only
at this location,
we're giving out free
Dark Core Deck Case replicas.
Huh, no way!
To be able to connect with
parallel worlds at will,
we developed the incredible
Dark Core Deck Case.
Although replicas,
they can still make
all the items and spells
that you'd use during
a Buddyfight game into reality.
For example, here's Gleipnir.
(marveling)
(screaming)
But the Dark Core Deck
Case's magnificent power
is reserved for kids only.
That means no adults allowed.
Now, don't be shy, take one,
and start using yours to
try and change the world
into a better place,
brought to you by
the very generous Mr. Gaen.
Oh, it's like a dream come true!
Hey, let me down,
I want one, too!
Akatsuki, no!
You should know how bad
those Dark Core Deck Cases are.
Remember Doai and
Shosetsu Kirisame?
Have you forgotten how
they were both controlled
by the dark power?
I know.
But if I had one,
I could become
an awesome fighter like you.
I could use Art
of Body Replacement
and Five Heavenly
Swords, Onimaru.
Seriously?
Easy, Zanya.
We all make mistakes, man.
Wait a sec.
Don't tell me you want to
let them get away with this.
They turned the power of
the cards into reality.
It makes sense that people
would want to try them out.
Yeah, but with everyone using
them, it's kinda dangerous.
And it's a little bit strange
that they can only
be used by kids.
It sounds to me like they're
planning to hand them out
as a way of finding some
new members for Disaster.
So you have to side with
them to use their power?
How does that make the
world a better place?
Is that supposed to be justice?
I can't believe Tasuku
was with these guys.
I wonder how he is.
You're right, Tasuku's lost it.
Hmm.
And it's up to us to stand
by and help our friends,
even when they've
made bad choices.
Yeah, man!
Hey, thanks for reminding me.
♪
Sword of Nothingness!
Distortion...
Punisher!!
♪
Uhh.
What could go up against
Distortion Punisher!!?
Don't waste your time
worrying about the impossible.
Tasuku created
that card himself,
and he's the only one
ever to have used it.
You can't defend against
what you don't know.
Did you just say that he
created a card by himself?
The Purgatory Knights
deck is my masterpiece.
I designed it around
Distortion Punisher!!'s
unique capabilities.
Are you telling me that
there's no way to counter it?
Most cards you can think
of are completely useless
against the powerful
counter final card,
especially counter spells.
Uh, oh.
Counter spells.
I see what you're talking about.
Uh?
Welcome back to
what's turned out to be
the most exciting
tournament of the year!
The third and final game of
the Gaen Cup Championship Round
is just moments away!
To recap, we've had one win
for Team Balle du Soleil
and one win for Team Purgatory.
The winner of this next
fight will be crowned
the Gaen Cup Champion!
Wow, this is the most riveting
tournament I've ever watched.
You got that right,
especially since Purgatory
Knight is really Tasuku.
And I just know that my big
bro's gonna win this one!
The final fighter
for Team Purgatory is,
as I'm sure you all know by now,
the great Tasuku Ryuenji!
Hey, down here!
I remember like
it was yesterday,
the day you and I had
our first Buddyfight.
You were the one who showed me.
You helped me to see how
majorly fun this game could be.
(shouting)
Jamadhar, you know what to do.
With pleasure.
(grunting)
♪
In honor of that game,
I'll try and make today's
fight as fun as possible.
You do realize I'm
not the same person
that I was back then.
I'm the Purgatory Knight.
Except for that armor,
you look the same to me.
You're wrong, Gao,
everything is different.
For me, this fight is a step
towards stopping injustice
and changing the world for good.
I can't just treat
it as some game.
Maybe you have changed.
The old Tasuku would
never have said that.
Why don't you get it?
Buddyfight is a game.
One of the coolest
games I've ever played.
And you're not
gonna ruin it for us!
I'll make you come
to your senses.
I'll make you see it
doesn't have to be this way!
It's time to wake up.
Eclipsing the
darkness with flames
and brightening the
hearts of the mistreated...
All right, yeah!
The Mighty Sun Fighter is here!
Now, let's get
this party started.
Oh, my, Gao just made his
Mighty Sun Fighter speech
for the very first time
during the Gaen Cup.
So what do you think it means?
To be perfectly honest,
I've never understood it all,
but there's one thing
I know for sure,
and that's when he becomes
the Mighty Sun Fighter,
there's definitely
something different about him,
and I mean that in a good way.
Big Z?
We decided to join you in here.
To cheer on Gao,
you know what I'm sayin'?
Thanks, guys.
The most powerful deck ever!
Blazing a path
toward the future!
Luminize, Explosive Dragon Fang!
A binding pact
made in shadows.
Arise, all knights of despair.
Dark Luminize,
Purgatory Knights Conviction!
Buddy...
Fight!
‐It's time to raise the flag!
I fight for Dragon World.
I'm with Darkness Dragon World.
Who knew smiling could
make your whole face hurt?
Why are you still here?
I'll leave, once I've watched
this fight through to the end.
Why waste your time?
It's obvious that Purgatory
Knight is going to win.
Tasuku has the first move.
Let's go to work.
I equip...
Purgatory Sword, Fatal.
♪
Just remember,
that Gargantua Punisher!!
Impact Card you're holding
is one that I created.
That's why I'll be
able to destroy it!
Take this!
Sword of Purgatory, Fatal!
(groaning)
End of move.
All right, Drum.
Looks like rest time is over.
No prob.
Let me at him!
Draw.
Charge and draw.
♪
Heads up, Tasuku.
I call Systemic Dagger
Dragon to the left,
and I Buddy Call
Drum to the right!
Okay, let's tear it up!
I call Boomerang Dragon
to the center.
Let me at him.
I equip Dragonblade, Drumsword.
♪
And I set Dragon Return System.
Time to unleash the next
generation Gao formation!
So far so good.
Yeah, bro.
We got it in the bag.
Time to do your thing.
Evolve into Super Armordragon,
Drum Breaker Dragon.
Attack!
(growling)
(screaming)
Super Armordragon,
Drum Breaker Dragon,
is in the house!
Smooth move!
Not only did he start
out by completing
the next generation
Gao formation,
but he also evolved
Drum into Drum Breaker!
Okay, Drum, you know
what to do next, right?
You better believe it.
Spinning Blasting
Assault, Mobile Ram,
Drill Ram Breaker!
♪
Let fly, Boomerang Dragon!
I'm going off like
a frog in a sock.
(grunting)
I'm a thunder from Down Under.
Now, Dagger, we'll
attack together.
Delightful, Danse Macabre!
♪
Huh?
(screaming)
I cast Black Dragon Shield!
End of move.
Gao's four‐in‐a‐row attack
took a huge chunk of life
points away from Tasuku.
But the former Buddy Cop
isn't even fazed!
He's so cool!
I cast Abyss Symphony.
This spell can only be cast
when a player has six
life points or fewer.
It lets you increase the
number of cards in your hand.
I call Purgatory Knights,
Silver Staff Dragon,
to the left,
and Buddy Call
Purgatory Knights Leader,
Demios Sword Dragon,
to the right.
♪
Who dares to challenge
my knightly power?
Not the guy who destroys
his own teammates.
That's right.
We gotta step up our game.
He's the best there is.
I call to the center
Purgatory Knights,
Crossbow Dragon.
Wow, amazing!
Tasuku's just called out
a Size 0 Purgatory
Knights monster.
What's next?
This could be trouble.
He's the one we
were worried about.
That dragon gets
one more attack
for each Purgatory Knights
monster he destroys.
That doesn't sound
very good to me.
Get ready for up to six
attacks coming our way.
I set Crush that Body,
and Sustain Mine.
It doesn't matter how
many shields we have.
It's not gonna be enough.
Come on, kid, you gotta
move me to the center!
Ugh.
You got it, go ahead, Drum.
♪
I'll hold 'em off.
Now, Demios.
Go attack the center.
The immortal and undefeated
Purgatory Knights.
Hyah, ha, ha!
Standing before us means
you accept your fate.
It's high time that
you learned your place,
child of the Drum tribe.
(grunting)
You were saying?
I've got one more card
in my soul, oh cocky one.
There's no way you're
getting rid of me that easy.
A Super Armordragon.
Your fighting style's
similar to mine.
Just as I thought.
You used to be one of us.
Continue the onslaught,
Silver Staff.
Attack the center!
With pride.
(grunting)
Still here, boys.
That's the last of the
cards in Drum's soul.
And now I'll activate
Demios Sword Dragon's ability.
Time to witness the
rule of Purgatory.
Run for your life.
Kanonas Katharterio!
Great Lord Demios,
may your victory be sweet.
(screaming)
♪
With the destruction of one
Purgatory Knight monster,
Purgatory Sword, Fatal's
critical is increased,
and Tasuku's set spell ability
increases his gauge by one.
By sacrificing
a Purgatory Knight monster,
he can attack one more time.
This will be his third attack.
Nin.
Now, Demios, attack
the center once again.
(growling)
(Drum groaning)
And now your soul is empty,
which means you will
fall into darkness.
Sorry, kid.
No, wait!
You can do this.
I know you can make
Tasuku see the light.
Excellent work
opening up the center.
Crossbow, attack the fighter.
(laughing)
This might sting a little.
(groaning)
My poisonous arrows
are super effective.
Now then, Demios, I'm ready.
Do what is necessary.
You show excellent resolve,
and now I'll play my part.
Kanonas Katharterio!
Long live the undefeated
Purgatory Knights.
(laughing)
Demios, prepare
for another strike.
Attack the fighter!
(grunting)
Demios Retribution!
Ahh!
Brutally, the fifth
attack of this turn
smashes Gao's life
points down to five.
And without a second to think,
the sixth attack is
coming hard and fast.
Get ready for the
Purgatory Strike!
Do something, bro.
You can't lose any more life.
I cast Blue Dragon Shield!
End of move.
Resisting the inevitable
will just prolong your misery.
Believe me, I don't want
to put you through that.
(growling)
Surviving six attacks, wow.
Indeed, but Tasuku
had no intention
of finishing Mikado off.
Yeah, he'd use his
Distortion Punisher!!
if he wanted to do that.
Everyone knows
there's only one way
that Tasuku could defeat Gao,
and that's by overcoming
his Roaring Slash!!
Gargantua Punisher!!
Obviously this has been
Kyoya's ultimate plan all along.
(portal whirring)
‐Huh?
Oh, no, what happened?
Are you all right?
I'm melting.
Who knew such
a thing could happen?
Run, run away.
It's not safe.
‐Huh?
‐What did you see?
Something that could end
the world as we know it.
Please, just go.
(portal whirring)
‐Huh?
Now I cast Dragonic Grimoire.
♪
Huh?
He just pulled Roaring Slash!!
Gargantua Punisher!!
But the Purgatory
Knight has six life.
There's no doubt he's got
Distortion Punisher!!
You're up, Boomerang.
Give the fighter a wake‐up call.
First I cast Purgatory Flame
that Resides Within the Body.
(grunting)
That spell gives up one
Purgatory Knights monster
and nullifies an opponent's
attack in exchange.
What's more, it causes damage
equivalent to the
sacrificed monster's critical!
♪
I'm not done yet.
Look alive, Dagger,
and attack Tasuku.
Danse Macabre!
Tasuku's down to
four life points,
which means Roaring Slash!!
Gargantua Punisher!!
can be activated.
(grunting)
Gao's Drumsword has
a critical of three,
which can only mean...
My Drumsword!
(groaning)
Tasuku has only one
life point remaining!
Is it all over?
What are you waiting for?
I've been well under five
life points for some time now.
You and I both know
that if your opponent
has five life points or less
and each of your centers
is open, then you can use
Roaring Slash!!
Gargantua Punisher!!
(groaning)
What will he choose?
Is Gao gonna use his
awesome Impact card?
Yes or no?
Aw, don't do it, yo.
If you roll with
your Impact card now,
that dude will use his
counter final on you for sure.
Gao's aware of his situation.
That's why he looks so worried.
He only has three life.
If Tasuku counters with his
Distortion Punisher!! card,
then Gao will definitely lose.
♪
If he doesn't have
a counter final card
in his hand,
we can win this,
but if he does,
nothing will beat it.
Especially counter spells.
Uh.
♪
I can't use that card right now.
I have to hold out
until next turn.
Play it, Gao.
Mm, really?
Yes, really, you gotta
unleash it right away.
Are you sure?
What about the counter final?
If Baku says to play it,
then I will.
He's the best deck
builder who ever lived!
Like always, I put
my trust in Baku
and in the entire
Team Balle du Soleil.
I owe them everything.
I guess that means it's
time for Final Phase.
I cast!
So this is how it's gonna end?
I'm disappointed in you, Gao.
Counter final!
I cast!
(clock ticking)
Let the world distort.
Turn back the sands of time and
erase all sadness from the past.
Sword of Nothingness!
Distortion...
Punisher!!
(loud crashing)
I'll be the one
to save this world.
Even someone like Gao Mikado
won't be able to stand
in the way of my triumph.
It's time for...
Tasuku and Gao's...
Card of the Day!
Today we're gonna talk
to you about a card
called Distortion Punisher!!
When your opponent has
four life points or less
and both of your center
positions are open,
this Impact card
deals four damage.
Pretty sweet, huh?
Don't forget that when your
opponent uses an Impact card,
it's possible you can
cause four damage
before it's even activated.
That's why it's called...
A counter final card.
So what do you think, guys?
You think you can
open up one of these?
You'll never know until you try!
♪
Next time, Kyoya's
plan is revealed,
the portal to Darkness
Dragon World has been opened,
and we find out why
Disaster made replicas
of the Dark Core Deck Cases.
Next episode: Eternal Rivals!
Join us for a Buddyfight!