Get ready for
a cool, new card game
that connects to
a parallel universe.
Special cards
act as portals
bringing monsters to earth
to become Buddies
with humans.
And through
friendship and courage,
help them take on
fight challenges.
It's called
"Buddyfight."
Really?
Sofia from the middle
school helped you?
Right, she was
actually pretty nice.
You cleaned up, congrats!
Yeah, thanks, guys.
I am in your debt.
But Gao, don't think
I'll go easy on you
in the final just because
you gave me a hand.
What would be the
fun in that, huh?
Sorry, Z‐Z,
I know I messed up.
It won't happen again.
Don't worry,
it's over with.
You meant no harm.
As for the deck,
just give it back
to the Seifukai.
Oh, okay.
This belongs to you.
Thanks, kid.
‐(sighs)
‐Huh?
What are you trying to pull?
The box is empty!
(exclaiming)
♪
(grunting)
I'll get us both
out of this dungeon
no matter what it takes.
(grunts)
♪
I may have kept my looks,
but age is wearing
on my skills, Doai.
It's not gonna work.
Come on!
I thought I told
you, it's no use.
Like the Mighty Sun Fighter,
the Seifukai
must keep calm.
The Mighty Sun Fighter?
I've been meaning
to tell you...
I met a kid in
elementary school
who goes by that name.
Really?
He's younger than us.
It's Gao Mikado.
Huh?
Of course.
‐Huh?
‐Here she comes.
♪
Hey, that's a Buddy Skill!
Vice President
Sofia Sakharov!
You mean to tell us
you're a Buddyfighter?
Not your business.
You know tomorrow's
the ABC Cup final.
Is that what you came
down here to talk about?
Competing in the match
will be Zanya Kisaragi
and Gao Mikado.
Or maybe you.
Huh?
Tell me, Genma,
wanna fight?
♪
There would be
one condition,
you must promise
to use this Dark Core.
What in the world is that?
Trust me, this core
holds more power
than any you've ever seen.
As the Seifukai leader,
I can't be seen
wielding something
so dangerous.
Only a special kind
of fighter is able
to handle the manipulative
forces of the Dark Core.
A strong and defiant leader
who can withstand
the sway of darkness.
(Doai screams)
Doai!
(grunts)
(struggling)
♪
Genma, I will see
to it that you use
this Dark Core.
You can do so voluntarily,
or we have ways
of convincing you.
♪
(punching)
‐(giggling)
‐Hey!
Stop that.
Come on, that's enough.
The Lord of Demons
does not whinny.
Yee‐haw!
I need to get a day job.
♪
Hm!
Whoa, man, you're
eating way too fast.
Huh?
Come on, bro,
your mom told us
to help ourselves
and eat what we wanted.
So, too bad.
Hey!
Give those back.
No chance.
(groans)
They're mine!
♪
Keep it up and neither
of you will be eating.
Whoa.
Watch out.
My mom's got
lightning reflexes.
Your mama, she's legit!
Thanks, I think.
I just wish Gao
would take his lessons
more seriously.
All he does lately
is Buddyfight.
Bro, quick question for you.
Did you ever ask
permission to fight?
Hm.
Nah, man, I can
tell she likes it.
Hey, who's this?
Oh, that's my brother, Yota.
You have an older brother?
You mean aside from me?
Where is he?
He's...
not with us anymore.
Oh, why didn't I know that?
Uh, oops!
(gasps)
How did that even happen?
Are you all right?
I feel terrible.
What can I do?
Please, don't worry about it.
It's just a frame.
Oh, man, that kid's
all kind of awkward.
You know what
I'm saying, yo?
Why you gotta be like that?
(groans)
Huh?
I can't hold on anymore.
That's gonna leave a mark.
I bet you he's
been spying on us
for his brother Zanya?
Are you sure that's it?
It's all good, guys.
Don't worry.
Better explain
yourself, bro.
That's so not what
I meant when I said
we should hang.
To be honest...
The thing is,
I heard that you all
went out looking for me
when I got lost the other day.
I just wanted to say thanks,
and that I'd like
to be your friend.
Hear that, guys?
Isn't that the sweetest?!
Don't sweat it, man.
There's really
no need to thank us.
Anyone want some?
(chatter)
‐Akatsuki!
‐Huh?
'Sup, Zanya?
Time to go, Akatsuki.
But they were nice to me.
Don't you think
a true ninja
should be nice back?
Ow, let go!
Sorry I didn't tell
you where I was going.
That hurts!
We're leaving.
Hey, what's with
the 'tude, bro?
Why are you being
such a buzz kill?
You got a problem?
It'd be great if
you could, I don't know,
maybe say good luck in
the big match tomorrow.
Whatever you say!
Just stay away from me!
Huh?
Hey, there's nothing
to be scared of.
You should come
on in and join us.
Even rivals can
chill together.
What?
We're not rivals.
Is that your idea
of a bad joke?
I give you two turns.
What's he talking about, yo?
It's trash talk.
Katana World players
pray on opponent's moves.
A one‐turn victory
is impossible.
So he thinks he can
beat us in two turns.
(growls)
Prey‐‐I'm a predator‐‐
Who cares about tomorrow.
Some final.
Genma's the one I
should be fighting against.
It makes sense.
You wanna face him
because he beat you
in last year's final.
It's about time
I proved myself.
I just gotta keep
getting better and better
with every match.
But this term it's a bit
of a gong show anyway.
Wait up!
Sorry, guys!
Bye.
What's Zanya's deal, yo?
I don't like him.
I'll teach him to be
afraid of the ladies.
I've never seen
Genma fight.
He must be pretty good.
I'd be bummed out
too if I couldn't
get a rematch against
the guy who beat me
in such a big fight.
(birds chirping)
Hmm.
(gasps)
Hey, Gao.
Thought I'd bring
the crew down
this morning to see
what you're up to.
We figured after last night
you'd be going
to look for Genma
and Doai.
(chuckles nervously)
I thought I'd try.
Well, we can help.
I'm not just good for rapping
and Buddyfighting, ya dig?
Not much time.
What are the chances
you'll be back in time
for your match?
I, uh, didn't
think about it.
I sure wouldn't
go out of my way
for Zanya, bro.
But knowing you,
you're gonna do it anyways.
I just get how it
feels to lose your rival.
You can't risk
missing the fight.
We'll take over the search.
Yeah, let us find
those disappearing
Seifukai, yo.
Wow, thanks.
You're the best, I‐‐
I guess we're helping too.
Huh?
Really?
You're even gross
in your sleep.
It's cool that you came.
I almost didn't,
but Baku made me.
Come on, the
sooner we find him,
the sooner this is
all over and I can
go back to sleep.
(chatter)
Huh?
That's the card that
Yota always carried.
I know.
I've always been so unsure
about this
Buddyfighting.
I guess I was afraid it
would push Gao and I apart.
It's strange.
Welcome to the
ABC Cup final.
For the very time ever,
two elementary school teams
will face off
for the trophy!
Let's meet the players.
From Team Kisaragi,
Buddyfighter Zanya Kisaragi!
And from Team
Balle du Soleil,
Buddyfighter Gao Mikado!
(crowd cheers)
♪
(message alert)
Huh?
Hmm.
(gasps)
Sword of Destiny,
pierce hearts
of darkness and evil.
Luminize.
Behold the Kisaragi ninja arts!
Just two turns.
That's all I need
to beat you.
Zanya!
Why are you so afraid
to call me a rival?!
I'm not, you just aren't.
It's just that
I'm kinda surprised.
When people started calling
me Tasuku Ryuenji's rival,
I started to like
Buddyfighting more than ever.
Having a rival is way cool.
It makes you wanna
fight even harder!
♪
Showering the sky with
scorching sun rockets.
Luminize!
Soleil Dragon deck.
Both fighters have
equipped their core gadgets.
Let's do this, people.
Buddy...
Fight!
(crowd cheers)
‐Time to raise the flag.
(groans)
Dragon World!
Katana World!
♪
First up is Gao.
Charge and draw.
You ready?
'Cause I am!
You find them?
(sighs)
All I found were
reasons to go home.
We got nothing, yo.
There's still a chance.
The Seifukai might
have better luck
than us with their search,
but it doesn't look good.
Huh?
(airy laugh)
Some rose‐colored
glasses would match
that outfit pretty
well, Magatsu.
Be positive.
The search isn't over yet.
What?
I thought we could
all go home now.
Think again.
Who invited her?
Wouldn't want a sample
of that laugh, yo.
My voice makes angels cry.
She's here to help Gao.
You know she's got
a thing for him.
You're just jealous, Magatsu.
Even if we were stuck
on a desert island,
you would be, um...
(whispering)
Ha!
You would be up the
lake without a paddle.
Epic fail at mixing
metaphors, huh.
Zip it!
But Gao does have
strange judgment.
Is this really
about a favor
for an opponent
he's about to fight?
The Sun Fighter
likes to get all up
in people's biz, yo.
Zanya wants revenge
against Genma
'cause Genma beat him
at last year's final,
so Gao's all like,
"Yo, let's do this."
(chuckles)
I think I might
know where he is.
Come on, follow me.
Gao's first turn
ends with a dud.
But Zanya's up next,
and he's already
called his secret weapon:
Phantom Ninja, Kashinkoji.
Activate Kashinkoji's ability.
With eyes everywhere
and all‐knowing powers,
Phantom Ninja Clairvoyance!
You know those
cards in your hand?
Yeah, they're showing.
‐Brother!
‐Huh?
It's just so intense.
Did you fall from
another ceiling?
No, not that.
‐It's about Gao.
‐Don't worry.
I'll take him out.
Why does everyone
think Gao's my rival?
This is a joke.
I think you're wrong, Big Z.
Huh!
Now, Shiden, go
and attack Dagger!
Right.
♪
Destructor Blade.
Kashinkoji, hit Gao
with your attack.
Gurenenbu...
with dragon breath
comes truth!
(grunts)
♪
Final phase.
Lethal Formation.
I had a feeling he
might pull that one.
♪
Set.
We have Green Dragon Shield
and Gargantua
Punisher in our hand.
He'll probably choose
a Secret Sword card
to counter their effects.
So then it'll either
be Star Crusher
for a spell or
Moon Fang for an impact,
but all we can do
is guess which one.
Hah.
This guy needs
some new material.
Yeah, maybe,
but it is a pretty
sweet technique.
It's still hard to defend
against even when you
know it's coming.
Who knew our school was so
seriously underground, yo.
My family's corporation
was instrumental in
the construction
of the Aibo Academy,
so I've always known
about the spectacular
secret passageway.
And you really think
he could be way down here?
You've looked everywhere else.
Besides, Mary Sue can
sense a Buddy monster.
Oh, then we must be
on the right track.
Okay!
Lead the way, Mary Sue.
How dare you!
What have you done to him?
Doai, stop this!
(growls)
I will not be part of
your impossible mission,
whatever it is!
♪
This can wait.
First let's deal
with our guests.
♪
Doai!
(grunts)
Even 100 demons couldn't
break through this!
So, what are we
gonna do, yo?
They have to be on
the other side.
Oh, so you brought
some dynamite?
Didn't think so.
(stone scraping)
Hm?
(Doai roars)
Watch it.
What do you think you're doing?
Heh.
Oh.
Double Sword,
go attack Kashinkoji!
Hya!
(screaming)
Thousand, you're up.
Attack Shiden.
(grunting)
Ha‐ha, cast!
Shooting Cross
Knives, Right‐Hand.
(grunts)
(shouts)
End of move.
Okay, this is getting
way too fierce right now.
Wow.
With a flick
of Zanya's wrist,
all of Gao's monsters
are eliminated.
Uh, what just happened?
Oh, snap, I should've
seen that coming!
Zanya played
a Right‐Hand spell card
when Gao was attacking
his right area.
The spell destroyed
all Gao's monsters.
Katana World has tons
of big‐time counter cards.
I should've given
Gao a major heads up
before the match.
My bad.
Time for my second turn.
And you have no
monsters to protect you.
Now I draw.
Charge and draw.
You're no match.
Shiden's effect.
Cyber analyze.
I discard one
ninja art card
from my hand and draw
two from the deck.
I call two Stealth Ninja,
Kirikakure Saizos
to the left
and the center,
Shiden and the left Saizo,
go teach the fighter a lesson.
(grunts)
♪
Saizo in the center,
prepare to attack.
Brother, wait!
What is it now?
It's your rival,
I‐‐I mean Gao.
He's trying to find Genma.
He would've even bailed
on the match to do it.
He feels so bad
that you missed out.
That's crazy, stop being
so gullible, Akatsuki.
Gao's right here
in front of me.
Honest, Gao's friends
are looking for Genma
right now!
That makes no sense.
Saizo, attack!
We can't afford to lose
any more life points.
Use your Green Dragon Shield.
But what if the Secret
Sword card Zanya set
with the Lethal Formation
is Star Crusher?
Well, I'm pretty sure
his focus will be on
stopping Gargantua Punisher.
Our spell cards
should get through.
What does Gao
think he's doing
looking for Genma?
He's so distracted
he's gonna fall
right into my trap.
Heh.
♪
End of move.
Huh?
So what?
You've decided that
your plan is to do
nothing at all?
Come on, kid!
That's not gonna work.
Zanya's gotten
inside your head.
Thought you were gonna
finish me in two turns.
Huh, it's true,
you are lucky.
Your move.
I don't know about that.
But I have a pretty good
hunch of what you're up to.
I call Thousand Rapier
Dragon to the right.
And Halberd Dragon
to the left.
I equip Steel Fist,
Dragoknuckle.
(shrieking)
(screams)
♪
‐Huh?
‐(Doai grunts)
Gao's mom has
got it going on.
Snap out of it, kid.
Get a hold of yourself!
My lady, are you hurt?
Tell me that
you're okay.
Talk about girl power.
This was unexpected.
Open up the center!
Leave it to me, master.
♪
Okay, Thousand, follow me!
Now the question on
everyone's mind,
is Gao getting ready to use
his Gargantua Punisher card?
Depending on the Secret
Sword card Zanya set
with his Lethal Formation,
Gao's next move could
be the last one of
this year's tournament.
Which Secret Sword
card did Zanya use?!
I know Shooting Star
is activated by an attack
using an item.
So that can't be it.
That leaves Star Crusher.
That's activated by spells.
And Moon Fang,
that's activated
by an impact card.
Guess I got a
50‐50 chance here.
But I've got a feeling
about this one.
Hmph.
♪
Huh?
Am I glad to see you.
Hm.
Now can we get
out of this place?
It gives me the creeps.
(slurps)
(sighs)
(rumbling)
Ah!
♪
(grunts)
Wh‐‐what's happening?
Think you can
hide from me, huh?
Where is the Koryukien?
Please, I can explain!
There won't be
any need for that.
‐Huh?
‐The Koryukien's here.
Just as you left it.
No, you can't
give it to him!
Come on, Buddy!
Let's show 'em the light!
(Shido shrieks)
Hey, Zanya.
You want me to think
the Secret Sword card
you set is Moon Fang
so that I won't
use Gargantua Punisher,
but my gut says you
used Star Crusher,
so I won't use a spell.
Prepare for final phase.
Ah!
Huh?
♪
It's Genma.
He made it.
He could've knocked.
What an entrance!
Genma Todoroki,
who's supposedly
been missing, is now here.
Interrupting the final match!
Gao, we found him, yo!
Huh?
Just so you know,
I'm gonna need
therapy after today.
(airy laugh)
You can thank me later, Gao.
You guys really came through.
Thanks, everyone.
I don't believe it.
They did this for me.
I should've
listened to you.
Hmph.
♪
Hey Mom, you missed the action.
(laughs)
‐Genma.
‐This is fantastic.
Where have you been?
Are you okay?
Silence!
Because of recent events
that I'll explain later,
as Seifukai leader,
I cannot approve
this final match.
Are you for real?
First you don't
bother showing up,
and now you actually
want us to redo
the whole tournament?
‐No!
‐Ugh!
I was being held
against my will
by the student council
president, Magoroku Shido.
Okay, okay.
Let's not exaggerate.
He's such a joker.
I'll make an exception since
you were last year's winner.
You can compete today,
but I will be
your opponent.
What?
The student council
president's changing
the rules?!
This tournament's
just full of surprises.
Hang on,
what about us?
We're in the middle
of a final here!
Don't worry.
You'll still
get your chance.
I'll be your opponent
once I finish off Shido.
Sounds good.
I can live with that.
Awesome news, hey Zanya?
You're gonna get to
fight Genma after all!
Yeah, but wait.
You were about to‐‐
It's not over.
You think so?
Maybe I almost had you.
But you never know till
it's over, am I right?
Besides, now I get
to fight Genma.
It's a win‐win.
A win‐win?
♪
I had Gao all wrong.
Hello there!
I'm Paruko, here
to guide you through
the world of Buddyfight.
Zanya's specialty
is called Lethal Formation.
It's a set impact
that can do a lot.
To use it, you gotta
guess your opponent's
strategy and then
choose one of three
different Secret Sword cards
and set it.
Shooting Star for an item,
Star Crusher for a spell,
and Moon Fang if you
think your opponent's
gonna use an impact card.
If you choose right,
you'll cause three damage.
Can you open a Buddy Rare card?
What do you think?
♪
Yikes, get a load of
Genma's Buddy monster.
Martial Arts Dragon
Emperor, Duel Sieger?
Wait till you see what
amazing abilities he has.
Next episode,
"Menacing Duel Sieger!"
Join us for a Buddyfight!