Do you have what it
takes to Buddyfight?
Choose your favorite
world and use special cards
to summon its powerful
monsters into reality.
Challenge other fighters,
and Buddy Call your toughest
ally to fight by your side.
Get ready to raise the flag!
(chittering)
I disagree, I have
faith in Tasuku.
Even if some momentary
lapse in judgment
led him to join this
Disaster or whatever,
I'm sure he'll
regain his senses soon.
‐How d'you know?
‐Call it feminine intuition.
I wonder if Gao Mikado
would agree with you.
Probably‐‐he's the
Mighty Sun Fighter.
He's always trying to see things
from others' perspectives,
but getting caught up in
other people's business
can cause you to lose your
focus and your motivation.
It's the same with Zanya
with his hero joining Disaster.
It's no surprise that
he's a little bit shaken up.
He's not himself because of it.
When I agreed to this,
I didn't think things
would get so weird.
They're just gonna
have to deal with it,
or everything we've
done will be for nothing!
‐Hmm.
‐Mmm.
♪
‐Yo, yo, yo, yo!
Guess what‐‐Gao's
super fly grandma
sent us all some care packages!
Get ready for
some serious eats!
Hey, are you
calling me a quitter?
You said the only reason
you're in this contest
is to see what happened
to Tasuku, did you not?
Wake up and smell
the goodness, yo!
I just said I wouldn't be
surprised if you backed out
now you know the truth.
Besides, I doubt you
could fight him properly
in your current
emotional state anyway.
Yeah, right‐‐you were
as shocked as anybody!
You think you could
fight him properly?
Hmm‐‐of course!
No matter who my opponent is,
I would fight them
with my full strength!
Even if it was...
someone I looked up
to since I was little.
Excuse me‐‐care package!
‐This means nothing now!
‐Hey, stop it!
He gave that to your
brother, not to you!
A girl just touched my shoulder!
‐Here.
‐Oh, thanks a lot, Kuguru.
Come on, let's
start on the new deck.
Adding Jack to the mix is
gonna take some time, kid.
A new deck with Jack in it?
What's he talking about, bro?
He's gonna help
to get Tasuku back.
He's gonna fight
alongside us in the semis.
What are you thinking?
You wanna mess with the
Explosive Dragon Fang deck?
It'll totally throw
its balance way off!
But I promised him, Baku!
Come on, please?
I wish I could, but
there's not enough time.
It's not possible to build
a deck with Jack in it now.
Even if I wanted to, I‐‐
That's not the
real reason, is it?
You're afraid of losing at
deck building, aren't you?
‐Huh?
Wanna explain that one for me?
To the deck builder for the
next team we're up against.
So, why don't you
become one of us?
‐What?
‐Darkness Dragon World has‐‐
Apparently, it's
someone Baku knows.
(gasping)
♪
Don't worry, you won't
have to think for yourselves.
The deck will show you
exactly what moves to make,
and if not, I'll give directions
myself from the Buddy Pit.
Asmodai is right.
There's a player on
Team Darkness Masterminds
named Gremlin.
He's my cousin, Retsu Omori.
He's the one who taught
me how to build decks.
‐Is that true?
‐Look, you gotta listen to me.
Our only hope is to
stick with the plan!
We can't beat them with a deck
that we put together in a rush.
No!
I have to fight with Jack.
Just put him in the deck
and leave the rest to me!
♪
Uh, testing, testing?
Just checking, can
everyone hear me okay?
The second semi‐final
match is about to begin!
Remember to turn off all cell
phones and personal devices.
If you're fighting next,
please make your
way to the stage now!
Okay, we're up.
Let's decide who will
be playing the first game.
Uh, hey, I'll go!
‐Are you serious?
‐I'll dance and lose
‐like a pro out there!
‐What do you mean "lose"?
That's crazy talk!
Be real, I'm no match for them.
♪ These two players,
they don't wanna fight ♪
♪ And the deck builders,
they're all uptight ♪
♪ So my boy Tets is
all on his lonely ♪
♪ With his bunk skills,
he's def goin' homie ♪
♪ But no sweat,
it's not all a loss ♪
♪ I'll show 'em my dance
moves are totally boss ♪
♪ We're going live
round the globe ♪
♪ Now move over and watch ♪
Maybe if you're lucky,
you'll catch the eye
of some head honcho producer,
and he'll sign you to
his big‐time record label!
Wow, that'd be sick!
Mhm!
I don't know.
♪ Team Balle du
Soleil is no more ♪
♪ Catch you later,
we're out the door ♪
♪ Though we're
breaking up, don't pout ♪
♪ Just be sure
to check me out ♪♪
What‐‐we're not breaking up!
♪
It can't be over.
I'll figure it out.
Welcome back, everyone!
I know you're as
excited as I am!
The second semi‐final match
of the Gaen Cup starts now!
And the first player
for Team Balle Du Soleil
is Tetsuya Kurodake
and his Buddy Asmodai!
Why would they
send him out first?
Don't know‐‐they must
have their reasons, though.
Let's hit it, Tets!
♪
(chanting "yo")
♪ We're dancing to my jam ♪
♪ Everybody knows who I am ♪
♪ Just throw your
hands in the air ♪
♪ And wiggle like
a special rare ♪
‐Buddy!
‐Fight!
(cheering)
Wow, that's the
hip‐hoppingest show
this reporter's ever seen!
Check your social
media for trending!
Is it me or does Tetsuya
seem different somehow?
How dare he?
(unintelligible)
my son Magoroku!
He'll pay for this!
Huh?
You're really working
up a sweat out here!
Just thought I'd cool ya off.
(groaning)
What's this‐‐Team
Darkness Masterminds'
first fighter Davide Yamazaki
has snuck onto the stage,
and it looks like he's trying
to get under the skin of
his opponent before the game!
Thanks, yo!
‐I needed a shower!
‐What?
He does seem a little
more confident than usual.
Even after all that
dancing he just did.
I sense a deeper focus in him.
I just hope the little
guy's not up to something.
Grind hearts into dust!
Dark Luminize, The Black Dragon!
A millennial kingdom, yo,
where you can play for ages.
Luminize, Devil's Millennium!
‐Yeah!
‐Let's start
this semi‐final
off right, everyone!
Buddy...fight!
‐Time to raise the flag!
I'm with Magic World!
I fight for
Darkness Dragon World!
♪
Davide will have the first turn!
What should I do?
Don't play around, focus.
Of course.
If you can just obey the deck
and not let yourself
get distracted,
then your victory is certain.
Yeah, yeah, okay,
Master Deck Builder.
I call to the center
Bloody Moon Dragon!
(roaring)
Come on, attack the fighter!
♪
End of move.
Tetsuya's up next,
but will he be any match
for the Darkness Dragon World?
There's no way
he's gonna win this.
Prove 'em wrong, Tetsuya.
Come on.
‐Your move.
‐All right, A‐Dawg,
‐here goes nothing!
‐Got you covered!
Let's get him!
Draw‐‐charge and draw, yo!
Let's just hope our little
strategy for saving the team
works as planned.
♪
I call Demon Sommelier,
Zagan to the center!
Merlot, anyone?
And to the left, I call
Demon Realm Architect, Gamigin!
What can I build
for you this time?
Could you hook me up with
another Solomon's Great Barrier?
You bet I can!
‐Think fast!
‐With that set spell,
all the size two
72 Pillars monsters
become size one monsters,
which means that he could
still call one more monster
that's size two or smaller!
And with Demon
Sommelier, Zagan's ability,
he can cast a one
gauge spell for free.
He is looking good!
Now I call to the
right, Sky Poet, Amon!
To fight or not to fight?
Lights, camera,
and it's show time!
(chanting "yo")
♪ We got you on the run ♪
♪ 'Cause we're number one ♪
♪ We got your back in
a Magic World attack ♪
Okay!
That's one out of the way!
‐A very bold choice!
‐Bold indeed!
(groaning)
♪
‐End of move.
‐Did you see that?
He might not lose after all!
No way it's gonna last, bro.
Your move.
Look at all the
72 Pillars monsters!
Two‐‐no, three!
(laughing)
All right, that's perfect,
because the more food there
is for my hungry dragons,
the happier they're gonna be!
Remember, your
opponent uses Magic World,
so don't even think about
leaving your center open
and attacking him directly.
You're so annoying!
Just sit back and
watch me kill it.
I'm gonna do what I
want from here on out.
‐No, wait!
‐I Buddy Call Death Dragon,
Death Gaze Dragon to the right!
Let's do this.
He regains one life point
thanks to a Buddy gift.
To the left, Black
Dragon, Spinechiller!
♪
(cackling)
And I equip Evil Death Scythe!
(laughing)
♪
What a fool.
He shouldn't leave
his center open!
(laughing)
Spectral Strike!
Huh‐‐ahh!
Okay, Death Gaze,
take out Gamigin!
♪
You're losing your spirit.
Spectral Strike,
Spectral Strike!
♪
Davide's Spectral Strike has
taken out all Tetsuya's monsters
and knocked him down to
just three life points!
This is fun!
(laughing)
And it's why I'll never
get tired of Buddyfights.
Tetsuya is literally
down and out!
Can he pick himself up
and make a comeback?
I highly doubt it, bro.
With only three life,
he's pretty much done for.
I don't know, I think Tetsuya
would disagree with you.
‐Huh?
I've gotta keep fighting
and hold out for my team, yo.
‐Tetsuya!
‐For shizzle!
If I gave up, I'd
just let everyone down.
Know what I'm saying?
Draw‐‐charge and draw!
Now I'm gonna call to the
center Great Duke, Astaroth!
Go, my homie!
Let's defeat some dragons.
I'm gonna keep going, yo.
I cast Nice One to
increase the cards in my hand.
I call to the left Fallen
Angel of Rage, Beleth.
Who gets it first‐‐tell me!
And to the right, I Buddy
Call Demon Lord, Asmodai!
(growling)
Boo‐yah!
Will the real demon
please stand up?
Tetsuya regains one life,
and with Asmodai's ability,
Tetsuya can discard
one card from his hand
‐and go for a‐‐
‐Dangerous Backdrop!
Oh, yeah, bring it, Asmodai!
One, two,
‐three, four!
‐Three, four!
All right, I want you to
throw your hands in the air...
And wave 'em like
a special rare!
Hip, hop, hip‐‐
There he goes again!
Maybe the live broadcast
has something to do
with the added
excitement in the stadium!
What's up with this guy?
Ugh, I showed him how
terrifying Spectral Strike is,
‐but he hasn't learned a thing!
‐I disagree.
There's a reason he's lined
up those particular monsters.
Huh‐‐but maybe‐‐
no, he couldn't have!
If we all get
together, we can't lose!
If we all dance
together, we can't lose.
Oh, man, I get it now.
I know what he means.
‐Huh‐‐what's that?
‐Yeah, what do you get, Baku?
It's simple, Tetsuya's
buying us time, bro.
He knows we're upset.
You guys about Tasuku
and me about how much
my cousin has changed.
He's just giving us
a break to refocus.
(gasping)
I promised my teammates
that I'd never give up,
no matter what.
Let's go, Beleth,
attack the fighter!
Finally, it's my turn!
You wish‐‐I cast Death Grip!
(grunting)
I can't seem to move.
But I still have
some moves left!
Attack him, Astaroth!
If you insist on
standing in my way,
then watch this!
♪
Twice is just as nice!
I can take it!
Us teammates gotta
stick together
and not get thrown off our game.
We just need a
chance to reenergize
so we can rise to victory!
You're right on the money, Tets.
Let's do this‐‐
Spinechiller Demon Dropkick!
I cast Devil Stigma!
♪
End of move.
If he's gonna be
destroyed anyway,
I might as well turn him into
life points and gauge for me!
Incredibly, Davide managed
to survive Tetsuya's attack!
And look at that!
Both players have just one
card remaining in their hands.
I can't remember a
more evenly matched game!
Oh, please.
I can practically...
You know you're on live TV?
I don't think you wanna do that.
There's no need to
resort to cheating.
Remember the probabilities‐‐
in your next draw
or charge and draw
you should pull a card
that will guarantee
you a victory.
Well, that is to say unless
you're exceptionally unlucky.
What?
That guy's a major
pain in the butt.
Whatever.
♪
I'll get a winning card in
my next draw, huh, Gremlin?
We'll just see.
Well, what do you know?
I call to the right, Great
Evil Dragon, Samael Apocalypse!
The hour of your demise is nigh!
Seven's better than one!
That's one gigantic monster!
Darn that guy's luck.
You gotta give his
deck builder credit.
'Kay, Gao, I hope
you don't mind, bro,
but I'm gonna chow
down before I pass out.
‐No, wait!
‐Don't worry,
I'll build your deck
right after I'm done!
Huh‐‐yeah!
What a move!
Davide destroyed Great
Duke, Astaroth's soul
using his Death Grip!
No biggie!
Samael, show this
bonehead your power!
(growling)
I cast Solomon's Shield!
I've gotta give him
just a little more time.
I know they'll come back
stronger than ever, yo!
I should eat, too.
Your appetite's back, huh?
Our friend's putting
himself out there,
fighting to save our team,
and we all owe it to him
‐to keep up our strength.
‐Nin!
You're right.
If you didn't know,
Samael has a double attack!
Fire of Impending Doom!
♪
‐Spectral Strike!
‐Ahh!
That's enough!
Nice try, but I've still
got some moves left in me.
Check it‐‐oh, yeah!
That's what I'd expect from
the future King of Magic World!
Glad our team's refocused.
The food of champions.
Tetsuya, I have some
good news for you!
You did great‐‐it worked!
Back to normal‐‐yay!
Tetsuya, you're the
best teammate ever!
'Kay, let's finish this!
Yeah, listen to my boy
here and pick up the pace!
Don't ever tell me what to do!
Hmm.
Lights out!
Game over.
Winner: Davide Yamazaki.
I can't believe you played
right into your opponent's hand.
If you'd obeyed my
deck from the start,
you'd have won easily and
avoided embarrassing yourself
‐and your teammates.
‐Shut up!
As long as I win, who cares?
Know‐it‐all.
We're up, Tsukikage.
Nin!
‐You sure?
‐Of course.
Besides, I know you
guys need more time
to build a new deck
with Jack in it.
Aw, yeah!
We need you to win, right?
Team Darkness Masterminds
has won the game!
Will they continue
their lucky streak
and advance to the finals?
Or will Team Balle du Soleil
be able to turn things around?
Huh‐‐we have a
video presentation?
When you think of the greatest
fighter of this generation,
only one name comes to mind.
He fights with
strength, intelligence,
and an artistic beauty,
and his name, Magoroku Shido.
‐You're kidding me.
‐No one told me
to bring my promo video.
Get ready for the player
you've all been waiting for.
Hit it!
Note that the first
letter of each line
spells out his name,
Magoroku Shido!
But where does his strength
and talent come from?
We talked to those
closest to him to find out.
My son was born to be a
world‐famous Buddyfighter.
I am Sueroku Shido of
the Buddy Card Office,
and the only one decent enough
to attend the press conference.
I knew he was special
when the first word
to come out of his
mouth was "Buddy."
The next word he spoke
was "Daddy," naturally.
Hmm, I guess I
didn't need to buy them
any more time after all.
Now then, I've
prepared a short video
of all his special moments
since the day he was born!
Okay, sorry to keep
you waiting for so long.
Magoroku Shido has arrived!
I promise a one‐turn victory!
You hear that‐‐and I
thought his dad was confident!
That's my boy out there!
Go get 'em!
This isn't that kind of deck.
End of move.
‐I, uh‐‐
‐Where's that one‐turn victory
he was talking about?
I have to say, that
fail was kind of epic!
Can I have a do‐over?
No do‐over for you.
‐You built it?
‐Well, if he's here,
I guess he did.
Zanya, Gao's all
good to go down here,
so hurry up and take him out.
Oh, my trap's already been set.
How dare you laugh
while playing against me?
♪
Now's my chance to finish this!
I Buddy Call Death Ruler,
Gallows to the center!
(cackling)
I can almost taste
the finals now.
Okay, Gallows,
attack the fighter!
‐I don't think so.
‐What's happening?
Looks like you've
fallen right into my trap.
That's impossible!
I've done everything I
possibly can to avoid it!
I pay three gauge and
activate Super Lethal Formation!
Secret Sword, Morning Star!
That tricky set spell.
It's activated when
an opponent's monster
with 3,000 power or
less attacks the fighter.
Stop transmitting this
broadcast immediately!
This fight is
hereby disqualified!
‐Daddy, save me!
‐I'm here for you, my son!
Aww, I almost feel compassion!
Oh, wait, no, I don't.
(screaming)
Game over.
Winner: Zanya Kisaragi.
He did it!
Never doubted it for a second!
We're up‐‐let's keep this going.
Both teams are tied
with one win apiece,
and the fate of
advancing to the final
hangs on the shoulders
of each team's leader!
‐It's time for...
‐Tasuku and Gao's...
‐...card of the day!
‐... card of the day!
Today we're gonna talk about
the Great Evil Dragon,
Samael Apocalypse.
It has 8,000 power
and a double attack!
And each time it destroys
an opponent's monster,
its Spectral Strike
ability causes two damage
to the opposing player!
It takes out your
opponent's monsters
and life points
at the same time!
That's what I call
an ace in the hole
for Darkness Dragon World.
So what do you think, guys?
You think you can
open up one of these?
You'll never know until you try!
♪
Next time, Gremlin rejects
Gao's new and improved
Explosive Dragon Fang deck!
Next episode, Master
versus Apprentice!
Death Tallica and
Explosive Dragon Fang!
Join us for a Buddyfight!