♪
Do you have what it
takes to Buddyfight?
Choose your favorite world
and use special cards
to summon its powerful
monsters into reality.
Challenge other fighters and
buddy call your toughest ally
to fight by your side.
Get ready to
raise the flag!
Stay away from me!
(giggling)
Another girl!
No, stop!
(groaning)
Real smooth, Zanya!
♪
Game over.
Winner: Suzuha Amonasuzu.
That was rather easy.
Girls freak me out.
♪
Honestly, how can
a simple renovation
be causing
so much noise?
With the Gaen Cup
commencing in three days,
I imagine they're in a hurry to
get the work completed, my lady.
Hmm! That's why those
ninny‐brains should have let
our company take
care of all the details.
We would have finished the
job without making a sound.
It's all so infuriating.
Come to think of it, so
is that Gaen Cup invitation.
It's no big surprise
they sent me one,
but the nerve of them
to assign me a team name.
I should be able
to choose my own!
I quite agree.
It was far too bold,
but I will say
they couldn't have selected a
better leader for the ladies.
And now they've got
me stuck down here
in this smelly,
underground maze again.
(giggling)
Really, there's a
buddy monster over there?
Let's go!
(gasps)
♪
Shall I call security?
No, I don't think
that'll be necessary.
This must be the
girl Buddyfighter
the anonymous
tip was about.
Get her out of
here right away.
Yes, my lady.
For those just tuning in,
the opening match between
Team Balle du Soleil
and Team Goddess,
saw Lady Suzuha overpower
a nervous looking
Zanya Kisaragi.
This means that Team Goddess
is just one win away
from moving on
to the next round.
If it's all right with you, I'd
like to return to headquarters.
I don't think it
wise to leave them
unsupervised
for much longer.
Do as you wish.
You know where to find me.
Whip those Buddy Cops
into shape, Commander.
The second match
is coming right up!
Team Balle du Soleil can't
afford to lose again.
We believe that their
team leader, Gao Mikado,
will be taking the
stage in this round,
but who will be
repping Team Goddess?
Here come the
fighters now!
Let's give them a cheer
that they won't forget.
Come on, let 'em
hear you outside!
(cheering)
(yawns)
We won't be seeing
any action for a while.
I wonder which other fighters
could be on Team Goddess.
Huh?
♪
I don't believe it!
This is a
personal insult.
The second fighter
for Team Goddess
is Aibo Academy seventh
grader Terumi Kuchinawa
and her buddy monster is
Gorgon Three Sisters, Medusa.
You seeing this, A‐dog?
Yeah, and if
Medusa's her buddy,
there's no doubt
that's the girl.
Hey, don't you ditch me!
Her Buddyfighting
history's unknown.
There's no record
of her participating
in any tournaments.
That's weird.
Have you ever seen
her around before?
No, I don't
know everyone, Dad!
I'm going to get an earful
from PR about this one.
No, it's fine.
Oh?
You never know.
We just might be in store
for a surprisingly
entertaining fight.
But if it turns out
that as you fear,
she's the sort of player who
will disappoint the audience,
well, we have ways
of dealing with her.
Now, who will be representing
Team Balle du Soleil
in the second match?
I have to win this fight.
It's the only way I'll
prove myself to Master Kyoya.
♪
Yes!
That music can
only mean one thing!
♪
It's Tetsuya Kurodake
and his buddy monster,
Demon Lord Asmodai!
In a surprise move, Team Balle
du Soleil sends out Tetsuya
instead of Gao as
their second fighter!
(growling)
I wonder why Gao
isn't fighting.
I hope he's not
underestimating her
just because she's
an unknown fighter.
He'd better have a really
good reason for skipping it,
that's for sure.
We made a good
call, didn't we?
Yeah.
(grunts)
‐Alright!
‐Hold on a sec, yo!
‐Hmm?
Sup, guys?
Why don't you let
me take this one?
Bro, I don't
think that's wise.
What's gotten into you?
You're freaking me out.
You do realize that
if you lose the match,
Gao won't even
get a chance to fight.
Don't be a hater!
‐I've so got this.
‐You do, huh?
Then, in that case,
listen up, peeps!
I nominate Tetsuya Kurdoake
for the next fight!
Cast your votes now
for Tetsuya Kurodake
to represent his team
in the next battle!
I'm still undecided.
What's got you
all revved up?
Hmm.
‐My heart, yo.
‐Go on.
Crazy, right?
I can't believe it,
but my heart's
dropping a sick new beat.
Maybe you should
get that checked out.
I get it.
Follow your dreams.
(gasping)
Just be sure
to win this one.
Go make us proud!
You're the best!
Thanks!
Now, we sit back
and enjoy the show.
It's Tetsuya
from the park!
Remember me?
‐Hmm!
‐That's harsh.
Well, I guess
you're not her type.
Based on the
awkward tension,
I'd say Tetsuya actually knows
this unknown female fighter.
Let's see if her
team leader, Lady Suzuha,
can shed any light
on their relationship.
Hello?
Sorry, but I don't
know a thing about her.
Talk about
bursting my bubble.
My investigation
led to dead ends.
She's a mystery.
(screaming)
Game over.
Winner:
Terumi Kuchinawa.
♪
I'm impressed you
managed to defeat
both of my tuners
with such ease.
That settles it.
I'm making you an official
member of Team Goddess.
What?
Is that a problem for you?
No, it's just I‐‐
You'd like to join but
you have some conditions.
Mm‐hmm.
You must promise not
to ask me about my past.
Does this have
something to do
with what happened to
you before I found you?
Lying unconscious in
the underground maze?
Yes.
Very well.
I promise I'll never
ask you to speak of it.
But I could sense that my
words didn't mean much to her.
I believe she only
accepted my invitation
because there was
something she was seeking.
Something she
needed to prove.
‐Time to raise the flag!
I fight for
Magic World, yo!
And I'm with
Legend World!
For those just joining us,
the second match is underway,
and Tetsuya will
be going first!
All I can say is that
you've got it going on!
Huh?
Terumi, this
one's for you!
♪
(grunts)
Mic check, mic check!
Wicka‐wicka‐what?
One, two.
Tets and A‐dog
in the house, y'all!
♪ We're dancing to my jam ♪
♪ Everybody knows who I am ♪
♪ Just throw your
hands in the air ♪
♪ And wiggle like
a special rare ♪
Please stop it!
First, I'm gonna call,
and who could be better,
Fallen Angel of Rage,
Beleth, to the center.
Who could I hit first?
Yo, yo!
Yo, yo, yo!
My head hurts!
Beleth, my man,
I'm counting on you
to make me look
good, you heard?
Macho power!
(screams)
End of move.
‐We are number one!
How many times do
I have to tell you?
Stop it with
that stupid singing!
(crowd gasps)
Just as we thought.
It's her all right.
(growling)
I'll show you.
You two try‐hards
asked for it.
I told you to never
come near me ever again!
What can I say?
The heart wants what
the heart wants, you know.
(crowd gasping)
This is truly amazing.
Terumi's appearance
is transformed
right before our eyes.
(gasps)
And what a
beauty she is!
Our mystery girl
really cleans up good.
FYI, we've learned that she's
currently serving double duty
as her middle school's
secretary of the student council
and its vice president.
Everyone knows the president
does all the work.
They'll see how useless she
is when she loses her match.
I don't know.
I hear she's
pretty tough.
Though I'm surprised
that she's even here.
When she went missing,
I assumed you'd banished
her to your dungeon.
What? That's ridiculous!
You'll get me in trouble
starting rumors like that!
Besides, if you must
know, I'm a pacifist.
(chuckles)
I wonder who's responsible for
letting her out of the maze.
Someone's been sticking their
nose where it doesn't belong!
Looks like an
interesting fight.
I certainly hope so.
As we were saying earlier,
in order to spread the
popularity of Buddyfighting,
maintaining high
ratings is paramount.
Miss Kuchinawa,
you've more than exceeded
my expectations this time.
Draw.
Charge and draw.
Are you sure about her?
I am.
See for yourself.
It's obvious.
The Dark Core has
completely accepted her.
With her potential, she'd be
a perfect fit for Disaster.
Even so, she's been
at it a while and yet,
continues to be
a disappointment.
(screaming)
End of move.
I've seen enough.
She won't amount
to anything.
You're making a mistake!
Huh?
I'll prove you wrong!
I have the power within!
See, I told you
she could do it.
She's awakened the Disaster
Force in record time.
That troublesome
girl was supposed
to fight
against Mikado.
But it doesn't
really matter now.
I have a new plan.
I draw!
Now, I charge and draw!
Come on.
This'll be
her last fight.
I call Stheno to the center,
and Euryale to the right!
Get rid of these
wannabes for good!
♪
Stheno has destroyed Beleth
and for those who don't know,
Euryale gains
a double attack
when there's a Gorgon
card on the field!
(screams)
‐One more time!
‐Represent!
She's rocking it!
End of move.
That girl is
way strong.
This is where
Tetsuya cranks it up.
Your move.
Time to flip the
script and draw.
Charge and draw!
I call to the center,
Great Duke Astoroth, go!
That monster has
a one card soul guard.
No matter what
you do, it's useless!
You could never
win against me!
Why don't you
just give up already?
I think she likes you.
Usually when girls get
this mad, it means something.
‐For real?
‐Huh?
Why are you telling him
such complete nonsense?
My mama always told me that
I should just be myself,
so that's how I roll!
I cast Nice One!
Astoroth's ability increases
the number of cards
in Tetsuya's
hand at no cost.
I knew he had it in him.
I call to the left position,
Demon Realm Architect, Gamigin.
(chuckling)
If you're calling me,
you must want a set spell.
So, what is it
you want me to build?
If it's cool,
could you hook me up
with a Solomon's
Great Barrier?
Yeah!
That spells changes all
Size Two 72 Pillars monsters
into Size One monsters!
Your wish is my command.
Think fast!
Hang on, he's
doing what?
Now, I'm gonna
call Sky Poet, Amon.
Oh, dear.
To fight or not to fight.
In a surprising turn of
events that defy the rules,
we've got two Size Two
monsters on the field!
Two, three, four!
Just throw your
hands in the air,
and wave 'em like
a special rare!
We got you on the run,
cause we're number one!
Wrecking Ball!
Sorry, Princess,
your reign has ended.
They're all destroyed,
but that's impossible.
Let's feast on some
Legend World slime.
I'm starved, and I eat
life points for breakfast.
Tetsuya unleashes a
furious counterattack.
Please, sir,
I want some more.
Astoroth's double
attack hits the spot.
End of move.
No one likes the taste
of their own medicine.
(crowd cheers)
Looking good, man!
Keep it up!
‐Yo, yo, yo, yo, yo!
Why are you being
so ridiculous?
‐Yo?
You mean "ridiculous"
in a good way, right?
How can you just go
around singing and dancing
without a care
in the world?
You need to learn to
start taking things
a little more seriously!
Nah, you got me all wrong!
I just want
to make sure
everyone who's
watching us has a good time,
and that's including
you, homeslice.
Is Buddyfighting
just some joke to you?
To me, it's my life,
my reason for living.
Let me introduce
your buddy.
Her name's Gorgon
Three Sisters, Medusa.
♪
I don't know
what to say.
Believe me, you don't
need to say a thing.
Join me and
we'll save the world.
Join you to do what?
Don't you want to
help people in need?
(gasps)
Yes, of course!
We'll have to do
something about your name.
Why?
What's wrong
with my name?
It needs to be
a little edgier.
Oh.
Something like Terumi.
Yes, that will
work nicely.
From now on, you'll
be Terumi Kuchinawa.
But, I‐‐
Don't worry about it.
What's in a name?
Nobody ever
remembers them anyways.
It's not like we're asking you
to change your hair color.
Besides, before
I discovered
your natural talent
for Buddyfighting,
no one even
knew you existed.
♪
‐You want to turn back?
‐Mm‐mm.
Then it's settled.
How wonderful, Master Kyoya
has found a use for you!
Right?
Yeah.
I have a reputation
to uphold.
If I can't be useful
to him here and now,
I'll go back to being
invisible like before.
He said that my Buddyfighting
power could save the world,
so I'll give
him all I've got.
‐Buddy call!
‐Huh?
I call to the center,
Gorgon Three Sisters, Medusa!
With her buddy gift,
she regains one life point.
I activate
Medusa's ability!
Then I discard
one Gorgon card,
and destroy all monsters
Size One or smaller.
Hey, your crush
is crushing us.
But Astoroth and
Amon are Size Two.
You're having
a brain freeze.
Thanks to Solomon's Great
Barrier, they're both Size One.
Whoa, I totally forgot, yo!
♪
Thanks to soul guard, Tetsuya
still has one monster standing.
The great warrior born with
a golden sword in hand.
I call Medusa's
son, Golden Blade,
Chrysaor to the
right position.
Show no mercy and
destroy them all!
It will be done.
Total annihilation!
When there are three or more
Gorgons in the drop zone,
Chrysaor gains
the ability to‐‐
Penetrate.
(grunts)
Are you still gonna keep dancing
to show everyone a good time?
Oh, yeah!
You can't shut
me down that easy!
Please, Medusa!
Stop this fool from
saying another word!
(grunts)
End of move.
I don't understand.
Why won't you just
let me destroy you
in peace,
you big jerk?
I know Buddyfighting
can be hard,
but you really shouldn't
let it get you so upset
that you start
crying about it.
Easy for you to say!
You have other things
like dancing in your life.
If you take Buddyfight
away from me,
I'd have nothing left.
No buddy, no name!
Come again?
I'm guessing that maybe Terumi
isn't even her real name.
Without Buddyfight,
I'd be a nobody.
I wouldn't even
have any friends.
♪
Not as long as
this guy's around.
‐What?
‐Ask Gao.
I wanted to fight
with you so bad
that I asked him to
switch places with me.
Buddyfight's not just
a game to me, you dig?
It's the coolest most
primo game in the world
cause it brought
us two together!
I buddy call
to the center,
my main homeboy,
Demon Lord Asmodai!
Boo‐yah!
Now, you're talking!
Y'all need some
demon up in here!
I know I don't have to tell
you who's in da house.
It's everybody's
favorite TV host, Asmodai!
This game's definitely a
solid way to make friends,
but if you don't give props to
the ones who have your back,
they won't stick around.
Not even your buddy,
am I right or am I right?
Right?
Hmm.
Take care of
her for me.
Wait, what are you doing?
Tetsuya discards
one card from his hand
so Asmodai can
take down Medusa.
Way to represent
out there, A‐dog!
Even though I plan
on beating you,
I still hope we
can chill later.
I feel like dancing!
Come on, hit it!
Yo, yo, yo, yo, yo, yo!
♪ It's about
making friends ♪
♪ That's the name
of this game ♪
♪ And when you get
into Buddyfight ♪
♪ You'll want
to do the same ♪
♪ Now put your
hands up in the air ♪
♪ Whoo whoo ♪
Yo, yo, yo,
yo, yo, yo!
Well, what do
you say, Terumi?
Let's show 'em
how it's done.
What? No!
Super high speed
demon spin!
(screaming)
Asmodai takes
off one damage point.
Was that even an attack?
(crowd laughing)
That's what I'm
talking about!
I cast Key of Solomon,
First Volume!
Final Phase!
Yo, yo!
Raise the roof!
You got this,
finish it!
I know it's cheesy, but I'm
gonna call the power of love.
Here!
‐I beat for you!
‐He's done it!
Game over.
Winner: Tetsuya Kurodake.
Oh, no, now I'm going
to lose everything,
but I‐‐ I don't care.
For the first time,
I'm having fun.
‐Alright!
Um?
Okay, now you just gotta
tell me your real name.
‐Hmm?
‐Don't leave me hanging!
I want to know everything
there is to know about you.
Come on, tell me!
So making friends is
what the game's all about.
This is what
I've been missing.
It's so fun!
(crowd cheering)
(laughs)
This ties things up for
one win a piece, bro.
And that's how it's done.
Told you so!
Which means that
we're up next, right?
Yep.
♪
The team lost,
but Terumi won.
Now she understands
Buddyfight.
An excellent
turn of events.
I'm so glad.
I think perhaps,
she's finally found what
she's always been seeking.
Would you excuse
us for a moment?
Yes, of course,
take your time.
It seems my first instincts
about Kuchinawa were right.
She's not quite Disaster
material after all.
I want you to
deal with her.
Da.
♪
It's a shame
you weren't able
to make the most
of your chance.
Just as I thought,
Master Kyoya was the one
who arranged for me
to join Team Goddess.
I'm taking back your
Dark Core and buddy monster.
But wait, I'd like
to say goodbye.
Do you mean it?
I thought you only
became my buddy
because these
guys forced you to.
After fighting together for
so long, we've become close.
I guess ours is
another friendship
that Buddyfight's
given you.
I hope we will
meet again one day.
Then do you think we could
become real buddies?
No chance.
Huh?
Now I'm going to
take back your name,
and all of your
memories too.
Wait, you can't!
I haven't told
him anything yet!
My real name
or about my past.
Please, I'm begging you!
Terumi!
I was kidding about
the dance lessons.
Yeah, come on, he was
just messing with you!
Huh?
‐Two o'clock, Tets.
‐Yeah, we found you!
Hey, where you been?
‐Do I know you?
‐Huh, what?
Are you messing
with me now?
You and I just had
a Buddyfight together.
What's a Buddyfight?
I don't understand.
Where am I and what
am I even doing here?
This is weird.
What's wrong
with her, A‐dog?
♪
If I had to guess,
it's like somehow
her memory's been erased.
This is terrible!
(groaning)
Huh?
Help me.
Can you please
tell me who I am?
♪
I don't know.
Not really.
Oh.
♪
Huh?
Where you headed so fast?
I'm not sure, but I feel like
I'm free to go anywhere I want.
See you around!
We should let her go.
I think that whatever
or whoever it was
that a hold over her
is now gone for good.
But she doesn't
remember our fight
or any of the awesome
stuff I did for her.
(grunting)
This is the worst
thing ever!
It's time for...
Tasuku and Gao's...
‐Card of the day!
Today, we're
gonna talk about
the Solomon's
Great Barrier card.
It brings a whole new strategy
to a 72 Pillars deck.
It's a set spell
that changes all
Size Two 72 Pillars monsters
into Size One monsters.
Until now,
you couldn't have
two Size Two monsters in
the field at the same time,
but now you can have
three if you want.
It sounds like a 72 Pillars
deck is where it's at.
So, what do
you think, guys?
You think you could
open up one of these?
You'll never
know until you try!
♪
Next time, it's the deciding
match against Team Goddess,
and they have a surprising
fighter in store for Gao
who knows all
of his strategies
and all the cards
in his deck.
How will he
win this one?
Next episode,
"Paruko Takes the Stage!"
Join us for
a Buddyfight!