♪
Get ready for a
cool new card game
that connects to a
parallel universe.
Special cards act as portals
bringing monsters to Earth
to become buddies with humans.
And through
friendship and courage,
help them take on
fight challenges.
It's called Buddyfight.
Steel Fist
Dragoknuckle!
♪
I don't believe it.
This is Jin Magatsu
we're talking about.
Oh.
It seems the skills
of your classmate
are far greater than
I had first thought.
So then you agree that this
is your new deck, right?
No, it's not mine.
This deck belongs to
team Balle du Soleil.
Right.
Blah‐blah‐blah,
teamwork, whatever.
Let's go eat.
All right.
I just had an idea.
Let's take the Soleil
from our team name
and call it Soleil Dragon Deck.
‐Yeah, I like it.
It's gonna be an
interesting tournament.
I can't wait to shred
those middle school guys
with this Soleil Dragon Deck.
♪
So ABC Cup...
...bring it on.
♪
Until about a year ago
I thought I could do
just about anything.
Wicked.
Look at all the
cards you've got.
Quite the collection.
Wow, dude, Dragon World?
And is that a
Dragon Knight deck?
Yeah, I really prefer
the Dragon Knights.
It's totally epic that
they fight riding dragons.
That's just one of the things
that gives them their reputation
as fearless heroes.
I mean, what's not to like?
But El Quixote's missing
from your collection.
There's no way I'd include him.
He's just some
lame, whacko old guy
who tried and failed
to be a real knight.
♪
So that's the deal.
I wanna switch.
What?
Where's your sense
of respect, boy?
You're being very
rude to Stella here.
Huh?
You know my name?
Yes, you welcomed me
when I first came here
to this world of yours.
Forgive me, but
it's a knight's duty
to protect a beautiful princess.
Oh, my.
You call yourself a knight?
I heard you thought
a dumb old windmill
was some giant monster.
You attacked it and
became a laughingstock.
You're misinformed.
Huh?
Imagine if that windmill really
had been a terrible monster.
I charged at it in order to
protect the things I hold dear.
If that's not
doing a knight's duty
then I don't know what is.
You see what I'm
dealing with here?
I don't want a nut
bar for a buddy.
And that's why I came here,
to swap buddies.
I see.
Well, we've never
had a case like this.
Once a buddy's been
assigned we can't change it.
Tasuku Ryuenji.
Yes.
Hey, you're Gao Mikado's
friend, aren't you?
Uh, let's see.
Kitten Shirt, right?
It's a tiger, not a kitten.
Forget it, what's the point?
All I wanna do is cancel
my buddy contract, okay?
Don't do it, kid.
So you're actually
going to wait and see
if you can draw
a buddy rare card?
Not even.
I'm finished.
After all, Buddyfight's
nothing but a game of luck.
Anyway, I'll be in
junior high next year.
So it's time to move on.
(alarm)
We've located the
missing criminal fighter.
Akaoni Konmae.
♪
He uses the Danger World
and his buddy monster
is Axe Dragon, Dorcas.
Takihara.
You and Tasuku take this one.
You better be careful.
He's pretty tough.
Roger that.
Somebody get me
Stella right away.
Sorry.
I've really gotta get going.
And I think it'd be a real
shame if you quit Buddyfighting.
♪
Really?
No, are you sure about that?
The card of heroes.
♪
As you know, the eight
school teams have been decided.
The ABC Cup gets
underway tomorrow.
So in true Aibo spirit
let's forget it's a fight
to the finish and have fun.
All right!
And FYI guys.
This party is brought to
you by the middle school
student council
president Makaroku Shido.
Now then, let's take
a moment to introduce
this year's participating teams.
Hey, uh...
Has anyone seem Team
Rising Tiger around?
I don't think Noboru
even came to school today.
Please welcome to the stage,
Team Tetsu and Dai.
With Demon Lord Asmodai
and Tetsuya Kurodake.
The coolest, hip‐hoppinest
team in the tourney, yo.
Is it wrong to let
these inferior teams
get their hopes up for
winning the tournament?
Anything can happen in battle.
You said so yourself.
What I said was
anything goes in battle.
Which is why I'm
definitely going to win.
Dibs on the chicken.
Uh‐uh, I don't think so.
I'll nab one of these then.
Nope, mine too.
Huh?
You snooze you lose, bro.
Why you!
Here, try these.
It's kind of weird
Noboru didn't show.
Maybe he's sick.
Hi, Gao!
Hello.
So uh, have you seen Noboru?
Actually no.
Greetings, Noboru Kodo.
Welcome to Buddy Police HQ.
I'm Commander I.
Uh, hey.
I'm not sure why I'm here.
I mean, isn't this
place top secret?
Yes, but there's something
I wanted you to see
before you decide to
stop Buddyfighting.
♪
He's cornered in Area G.
I lost them.
♪
Whoa, what's going on?
Look who fell
right into our trap.
I guess in your haste
you failed to notice
the barrier generator above you.
You dirty...
You're gonna pay!
Come on!
♪
As I see it you
have two options.
You can give yourself up
or you can Buddyfight me.
Bring it on, you punk.
I'll make you tremble.
Monster Festival luminize.
Oh, yeah.
Tell me that's not
really your core gadget.
Stop it, Jack.
You shouldn't laugh at people.
(laughing)
Stop making fun of me.
Hurry up and luminize your deck.
Assemble, Dragon Army!
Dragonic Force, luminize!
Akaoni Konmae
targets buddy cards.
He's an infamous criminal
who steals rare cards
and sells them on
the black market.
What's Tasuku doing out there?
You know, if this guy's
so dangerous and all.
Don't worry.
Tasuku's doing
exactly what he wants to.
Huh?
♪
Let me fill you in
on his background.
It would be almost
four years ago now.
During the disaster he found
himself alone for three days
walking aimlessly
through the harsh mountains.
During that time
he says he came to a realization
that adults and
society in general
have heavily sheltered
him and children like him.
He wants to be able
to take care of himself
and make his own decisions.
♪
He met his buddy monster,
Jackknife Dragon,
and soon decided to go from
someone who needs protection
to someone who can provide it.
All right, Axe Dragon, Dorcas.
Go and attack
Bronze Shield Dragon.
♪
At first we were
rather skeptical.
But he convinced us all that he
was definitely more than capable
of carrying a
Buddy Police Shield.
I cast Dragoenergy.
♪
Okay.
Then I'll use a link attack.
End of move.
I used three monsters,
but I could barely
defeat even one of his.
Your move.
Draw.
Charge and draw.
I call Latale Shield
Dragon to the left.
Dragonblade Dragobrave!
♪
You're forgetting I've
got Dorcas at the center.
Your buddy won't be able
to break past her, ya punk.
Ready?
Yeah.
Okay, Jackknife.
Unfold first form!
Become one with the lightning
and strike him
down with your power!
Jackknife Thunder Storm!
♪
Oh, he made his dragon evolve.
You mean there's a
card that can do that?
There is.
But Tasuku's the only one
who has mastered it.
What, are you serious?
Use six life points.
That's crazy talk.
♪
Let him have it, Jack!
Thunder Rain!
♪
Oh, man.
I've been thunderstruck.
Latale.
Attack now.
♪
Thunder Blaster!
Dragobrave!
♪
Way cool.
The situation is now
under control, Sir.
Well done.
Let's reconvene at HQ.
Roger that.
Crazy.
He didn't even take any damage.
That's true, but to
increase his strength
he gave half his life
to his buddy monster.
I think Tasuku's trying
to grow up too fast.
And that drives
him to take risks
when he really doesn't have to.
He should be enjoying
his childhood more.
Maybe you could hang
out with him, Noboru,
and try to help
loosen him up a little.
Get his mind off the real
world and do kid stuff.
El Quixote.
Forgive me, I hope it
wasn't something I said.
It's hard to say, he
can be a little touchy.
Well then, let's go, boy.
The nerve of that guy.
He doesn't know me.
Ladies and gentlemen
and dudes of all ages,
to commemorate the
ABC Cup this year
we've ordered 100,000
Buddyfight cards.
In fact, my buddy's
actually on his way here
with them right now.
♪
(humming)
I think Noboru's got his
cell phone turned off.
He's not at home either.
Maybe he ran away.
What makes you think that?
He's the second ranked fighter.
And he hasn't fought
Zanya in a while.
You'd think he'd wanna challenge
the top ranked
guy, wouldn't you?
In the tournament
he'll face you.
That kid, Tetsuya who
he's already lost to,
and let's not forget Zanya.
If you ask me, the guy must
be a nervous wreck by now.
He's probably convinced himself
that if he competes
he'll be thrown for sure.
Thrown?
He means defeated.
Come on.
The fact the guy's not
here just proves I'm right.
He's got a point.
If he thinks he's gonna
lose he might not compete.
He's not the type to do that.
He's a hard worker,
always beating me at soccer
and on tests at school.
(gasping)
Look guys, Lady Suzuha Amanosuzu
has brought cake for everyone!
Lady Amanosuzu.
Thank you very much.
I must say that's
very thoughtful of you.
How delightful.
♪
Gao, this stuff they
call cake's delicious.
Life's nothing
but a game of luck.
What are you talking about?
Huh?
You heard what they said.
Tasuku's got that
whole tragic past.
♪
He and Gao are special somehow.
I'm not like them.
There's no way a guy
like me could win.
I just got dealt a bad hand.
♪
Listen to yourself.
Tell me, boy.
Do you know what the
second most popular book
in this world is?
What are you talking about?
It is said to be "Don Quixote",
a famous book that
is named after me.
Are you serious?
So why would people
read about an old man who,
according to you,
is just an old whacko
that never did anything?
It's because people
can relate to me.
I may chase impossible dreams
and seem crazy to some.
But by ignoring what
others think of me
and doing what makes me happy
I have lived a full
life with no regrets.
You see, happiness is finding
something you really want to do
and giving it your
all to be successful.
It's what determines
your true character.
Tell me, Noboru.
Do you have something
that you really want to do?
Uh...
Shake a leg, we're
in a hurry here.
Who's that?
I don't wanna be
a bad guy anymore.
Relax, my brother promised
that he'd keep the
Buddy Police busy.
Come on, we gotta go.
Give me the buddy skill.
I said I'm not gonna.
Think they're talking about that
criminal fighter from before?
Hey, you, what are you up to?
Are you crazy?
Making your buddy
monster help you
break the laws of the land.
As a knight I cannot
allow such a travesty.
I only helped because I
thought it was just a game.
But I'm done with evil.
Huh?
There's no way I
can get the job done
without my buddy skill.
♪
Akaoni Konmae has
a younger brother?
Yes, Aooni Konmae.
His buddy monster's Gaelcorga.
A hundred thousand
Buddyfight cards
are being delivered
to Castle today.
Then that must be their plan.
They were just using
Akaoni as a decoy.
Both of you head
to Castle at once.
♪
Hey, be careful.
What's the threat, bub?
What do you want anyway?
♪
You're a
Buddyfighter, aren't you?
I challenge you.
If you win I'll hand
over my buddy rare card.
But if I win you gotta
give me your buddy rare
no questions asked.
We accept.
What?
Need I remind you that this
guy's a criminal fighter?
You'd rather give
up without a fight?
You plan to live your
whole life that way?
I'm not saying that.
Enough talk.
Now let's do this.
First Full Class
Dinosaur Festival!
Luminize!
Come on, kid, hurry
up and luminize.
Luminize!
Knight Force!
‐Time to raise the flag.
I use Dragon World.
I fight for Danger World.
♪
What gives?
As of now I'm canceling
our buddy contract.
I'm returning to my world.
Gaelcorga!
Argh!
I'm gonna win this fight
and get my hands on
a new buddy, you punk.
Hey, someone's
Buddyfighting on the stage.
Isn't that the second
ranked fighter at Aibo?
Noboru?
What, let me take a look.
Where are you going?
I buddy call Gaelcorga
to the right position.
Or I was gonna do that
until the traitor bailed
leaving me to fend for myself.
Call.
♪
I'm gonna crush you!
Ogre!
♪
Take that!
End of move.
♪
Everyone, get back.
This guy's a criminal fighter.
So why is Noboru taking him on?
My guess?
He's probably being
forced to fight.
I call Red Baron to the left.
And I buddy call
El Quixote to the right.
I pay two gauge
to equip Twin
Dragonblades Dragoanthem.
♪
You're mine, thief.
I've always admired
the Dragon Knights
and dreamed of becoming one.
I now know that I can't,
but at least I get to
fight alongside them.
And even though I'm not a hero,
this game sure makes
me feel like one.
Hey, I get it.
This is what I really wanna do.
♪
El Quixote, attack the fighter.
Dulcinea!
With forged steel and courage.
Red Baron, attack.
Take that you swine!
Argh!
Get ready!
♪
I think the boy's found himself.
I have no choice but
to stop the match.
You can't!
Noboru's about to win!
You don't know that for sure.
I know he won't lose
to a criminal fighter.
Give him a chance.
It's your call.
If we intervene there's a
fair chance Aooni will escape.
I want to wait and
see how this plays out.
Well, let's be ready.
End of move.
If Red Baron hadn't
moved in to protect you
I'd have crushed you, you punk.
You just got lucky!
Your move.
Draw!
Charge and draw.
♪
Luck has nothing to do with it.
It's all about the
fighting style we choose.
I call Dragon Knight
Masamune to the left.
I'm gonna take this to the
final phase without attacking.
What?
I'll pay four gauge.
I cast.
When I attack with two
Dragon Knights by my side
it's a combined three man
special Dragon Knight technique
called Ultimate Smash!
No!
♪
Game over.
Winner, Noboru Kodo.
He just defeated a
criminal fighter, huh?
I told you, didn't I?
He's wicked strong.
Hey, watch out.
Huh?
Give me your buddy!
Buddy skill on.
Oh!
Uh, El Quixote, what's this?
Nice card fight!
Nah, that guy wasn't so tough.
Uh, Noboru.
What's that glowing
armor you're wearing?
It's a buddy skill.
Am I right?
El Quixote?
A buddy skill?
How come Asmodai hasn't hooked
a buddy up with some of that?
Aw, how am I gonna win the
Cup without crazy powers?
Yeah, he's right, man.
You're definitely
the guy to beat now.
Yeah, well, you can try.
I guess Buddyfighting's
my thing after all.
Uh?
All right.
I just hope we get
to meet in the finals.
Yeah.
Hey, dudes, the new
cards have just arrived.
So, you were way
off about this kid.
Guess so.
I underestimated him.
Now anyone's capable
of winning this thing.
You could be in big
trouble, Mr. President.
♪
It's all playing out exactly
as I predicted it would.
Hello there, I'm Paruko
here to guide you through
the world of Buddyfight.
When someone opens
a buddy rare card
the Buddy Police
pick up on the signal
and deliver a core deck
case to them right away.
The Buddy Police do
all kinds of things
and some of it's dangerous.
Like arresting rogue
criminal fighters.
Pretty cool, huh?
And they even keep an eye out
on all of the monsters
that come to Earth
looking for a buddy.
What do you think, guys?
Can you open a Buddy Rare card?
Join us next time
to see seventh grader
Suzuha Amanosuzu and Mary Sue,
her amazing buddy.
They say there's
nothing she can't do.
Next episode, the start
of the Aibo Buddy Cup.
It's gonna be a splash!