Get ready for a
cool new card game
that connects to a
parallel universe.
Special cards act as portals,
bringing monsters to Earth
to become buddies with humans,
and through
friendship and courage,
help them take on
fight challenges.
It's called Buddyfight!
Because of your blatant
disregard for protocol,
I will now oversee all
Buddy Police operations,
and effective immediately,
Tasuku's prohibited from using
Buddyfight cards
for one month.
Good boy.
Now hand over your
core deck case.
♪
We'll need your Buddy, too.
Hmm.
Well, I've been waiting
for the right time,
but now's as good as any.
I've been asked to go
teach in North America.
You're kidding me, right?
You're leaving for real?
Dad, come on, say something!
I think she should go.
She'd already be over there
if she wasn't so
worried about you guys.
On second thought, I really
think you should go!
You don't have
to worry about us.
Besides, I'm sure those
kids will teach you
how to be an even cooler mom.
I'm glad you understand.
♪
(indistinct chattering)
I still can't believe
a special rare
card's in that case.
I wonder which one
it actually is.
Word, guys, I just found out
what first‐place prize is.
It's the special
rare card, yo.
Who wants a piece
of this first?
Oh, over here!
I'd like to give it a shot.
(laughing)
I know Tets is a small fry,
but you sure you want
to take on a demon?
What he said, yo.
Huh, a small fry?
Why are you harshing
on me, A‐Dawg?
Just as I thought.
There are no decent
fighters here.
Says who?
This table's taken.
Hey!
Mommy, look at me!
Don't get a burn.
Have the
preparations been made?
Of course.
Exactly as you asked.
All that's left to do is...
(chuckles)
...sit back and watch as
the entertainment unfolds.
(horn blaring)
(gull squawking)
(roaring)
♪
Did you say the
Gaen Financial Group?
Yes, that's right.
You've all been invited
to their annual party.
This year, it's on
their special yacht.
I hear it's where all the
celebs and high rollers
hang out and hold one‐day
Buddyfight mini challenges, yo.
Buddyfight Weekly
said there's gonna be
a special rare card
on board this time.
It all sounds awesome.
So what is this
Gaen Financial Group?
Ah!
Uh, you mean you
really don't know, bro?
Have you been living
in a cave, my boy?
(laughing)
Oh, Gao, you're so strange.
If you want, I could
totally fix you.
LOL, as they say.
I personally like being
strange, but thanks.
(chuckles)
Among other things,
the Gaen Financial Group
manufactures core deck cases.
Daddy says the company
has been a major player
in helping to stabilize
the global economy.
Kyoya texted me himself,
and told me he wanted to
invite all the participants
from this year's ABC Cup.
Who's Kyoya?
Kyoya Gaen's the kid
who runs the company.
I hear his money has money.
Who cares, bro?
The Gaen Financial Group also
happens to fund Aibo Academy.
Ugh, I don't know
about you guys,
but rubbing shoulders
with those bigwigs
sounds like a major
snore‐fest to me.
So you won't be going then?
Mm, you couldn't
drag me there.
Ha‐ha‐ha, all right,
this is what I call a party.
I clearly heard you say
you wouldn't be coming.
It's not in his DNA to
pass up a free lunch.
♪
Pay attention.
Watch very closely and learn
from their many mistakes.
Hey, Zanya, Akatsuki!
Pretty swank party, huh?
Ha, my other plans cancelled.
I call the fierce
Armorknight Black Drake
to the center position!
Doesn't he know by starting
with a size three monster
he can't call any
other monsters?
That's such a rookie mistake.
That's not actually true, A. K.
Next, I call guard
to the right
and Armorknight
Eagle to the left!
(gasping)
If they're size zero, he can
call as many as he wants.
Kiri's getting
to be a real bro.
Just check his formation.
If he's getting
kudos from you guys,
I guess he's gotta be doing
something right out there.
So he's using Armorknights
and a few size zero
Duel Dragons.
Looks like your
basic hybrid deck.
I always get destroyed!
Quick, Armorknights Eagle
and Drake, attack the fighter!
Eagle bombardment!
To powder and dust!
End of move.
(coughing)
I'm down to five life points?
The writing's on the wall.
You know, I don't think so.
The cool thing about Tetsuya
is that each time he
fights, he gets better.
Keep watching and see.
Stronger each match.
That's gonna be me soon.
Someone order a
dangerous backdrop?
No, not Black Drake!
My homies have found
their rhythm, yo.
‐Yes.
‐Yo!
‐And we don't stop.
Yo, yo, yo, yo!
Ah!
End of move.
Ugh!
Why am I losing already?
‐Huh?
‐Your move.
I know I can do this.
I draw.
Charge and draw!
Is he doing what
I think he's doing?
I call to the center
Fighting Dragon, Demongodol!
Go, devour Eagle!
Ah!
I knew it!
I'm impressed, in no time,
Kiri's really mastered
the Danger World's
fighting style.
Demongodol has
double Soulguard
and a lethal counterattack
if he's not destroyed.
Tetsuya better be ready.
No doubt.
Remind me again why it's so
important for me to be here.
I already told you why.
As part of your
suspension agreement
you're required to help
our PR promote the game.
(grunting)
(whirring)
Tasuku, don't let
him get to you.
It'll all be over
before you know it.
I'm suddenly not
feeling so well.
I need to get some fresh air.
Don't be long, we need
you front and center.
Hi, Daddy.
I didn't expect
to see you here.
Magaroku, why, I'm here on
official business, of course.
What are you doing
hiding under the table?
Planning some grand entrance
as this year's
ABC Cup champion?
You should be the
center of attention.
Wh‐‐what's wrong?
Are you crying?
You did win the
trophy, didn't you?
Oh, Daddy!
They didn't let me win!
Okay, watch the uniform.
Tasuku, you're here!
I didn't think you'd show.
You took time out of
your busy schedule
just to see me?
‐Huh?
‐Hey, Gao.
I was hoping I'd
run into you here.
S'up, man?
He completely ignored me,
or was he just pretending?
Yes, of course,
as I'm the only daughter
of the famous
Amanosuzu family,
he wants to protect
my reputation
from those nasty
rumors in the tabloids.
Poor Lady Suzuha,
so innocent.
I cast Great Spell Saturday
Night Devil Fever, yo!
Great Spell Saturday
Night Devil Fever?
The fever, it's used
when there's six or more
72 Pillar monsters
in the drop zone.
And it lets you call
three size one monsters
of the 72 Pillars without
having to pay any cost at all.
And since he was getting
majorly squashed out there,
his drop zone's
loaded with them.
Stayin' alive.
Yeah!
Check it.
Saturday Night Devil Fever.
I'll get rid of a card and
activate Asmodai's skill, yo.
Oh, no.
Dangerous backdrop for what!
Come on, feel the beat,
and attack the fighter, yo.
Yo, yo, yo, yo!
Ahh!
Game over.
Winner, Tetsuya Kurodake.
‐One down.
‐That card's practically ours.
Well, that wasn't
a great fight.
Oh, I don't know.
I actually found it
quite interesting,
especially that little guy
who used the Danger World.
You mean Kiri Hyoryu?
If he finds a buddy monster
that fits his fighting style,
he'll definitely be someone
we'll need to
keep our eye on.
♪
Huh, so that's the head of
the Gaen Financial Group?
He's not very old, is he?
Apparently he's quite good
at Buddyfighting too.
You could say the
guy has it all.
What gives?
Why aren't you getting
Tasuku's autograph?
He's been your hero for
as long as I can remember.
Sure, I admire
his achievements,
but I don't get starstruck.
I'd never ask for an
autograph like some lame‐o.
Okay, got ya.
Huh?
But if you wanted to get one,
that'd be totally cool.
Good afternoon.
Thank you all so much
for coming today.
As a major fan,
I think it's wonderful
we can all come together
through friendship and courage
to enjoy a Buddyfight.
He has such a charming smile.
I don't know if
"charming" is the word.
Looks kind of sketchy to me.
Envy much?
Green clashes with pink.
Ugh.
I sure hope you all
have a good time
and enjoy the matches.
As promised, the player
who impresses me
the most out there
will receive
this much sought‐after
special rare card.
Now, let's see the
exceptional card
you could win.
(gasping)
Come on, is this
some kind of a joke?
(indistinct chattering)
I don't understand,
how could it go missing?
Oh, my.
Now things are gonna
get interesting.
There's been a crime.
Here you are, stay in school.
I gotta go, duty calls.
My brother's
your biggest fan!
Excellent.
This'll be even
better than I planned.
Excuse me, may I
examine that case?
Be my guest.
It's Ryuenji, isn't it?
Yes, and you seem to be the
victim of a serious theft.
(grunting)
When the ship raised anchor,
the card was definitely in
the case, is that correct?
Yes, I made sure
of it myself.
So the theft occurred
sometime after we set sail,
which means that the
perp is still on board.
Your reasoning
would seem sound.
It's such a treat
to see him in action.
Oh, Tasuku,
you're so wonderful.
The case doesn't look
like it was forced open.
I don't know how they did it.
I had a security detail
watching it the whole time.
There's no way
anyone could have
gotten close enough
to steal it.
You seem to be forgetting
one important thing.
Most of the people you invited
here today are Buddyfighters
which means...
...there are lots of
Buddy Monsters on board.
(laughing)
Though it's impossible
for us humans,
some buddy monsters have
the power of invisibility.
They could have
easily taken the card
from right under our noses.
Are you trying to say there's
a criminal fighter among us?
Tell me, A‐Dawg, did you?
Don't get it twisted.
It wasn't me.
I even have witnesses.
I swear Asmodai was totally
with me the entire time.
‐Me too.
‐Y'all sound
kind of suspicious, yo.
I wouldn't put it past him.
If anyone's good at sneaking
around, it's you, ninja!
Things are getting
heated out there.
Huh?
Oh, could that be
the missing card?
♪
Ah, unhand me,
you circus clown!
Ah!
What kind of card is this?
Oh, this is a total drag.
They might make the
thieves walk the plank.
Rules are different at sea.
I don't care, Drum.
Ha, I bet it wasn't even a
great card in the first place.
Don't you think
they'll find it?
Why would I care?
I'm sure the only thing that's
special about it is its name.
It's probably some
ridiculous, crazy‐looking,
coward kind of monster.
Hmm?
He's right, it may not want
to show itself in public
'cause of how ugly it is.
Who are you calling ugly?
♪
Ha, man, that worked
like a charm.
You're kidding me.
Oh, that guy, I met him
under the table a while back.
(shouting)
Greetings.
I'm the Dragowizard Qinus
Axia, at your service.
A Dragowizard?
A dragon that hails
from Magic World.
One of its abilities is to
directly damage the fighter,
so I'd say it more than
qualifies as special.
You there, speak up, who
stole you from your case?
Who says I was stolen?
I decided to escape
all on my own.
Ah!
As a fellow dragon,
you must understand.
Meeting your buddy
should be magical
like finding your soul mate,
but they're giving me away
like a carnival prize.
What if I don't even like
the player they give me to?
I refuse to go
along with this.
It's just not fair.
A fellow dragon, huh?
You're nothing like me.
You Armordragons always
focus on the small things.
It's not a small thing!
Gao, I'm curious, did
you do that on purpose
'cause you knew that the
card wasn't really stolen?
Sorta, I didn't
know for sure,
but you could say
I had a hunch.
No self‐respecting
Buddyfighter would stoop
to stealing the
first‐place prize.
That doesn't explain how you
knew the special rare card
would be a monster.
Jin's right, it could
have been a spell
or an item card
inside the case.
Those wouldn't be able to
just disappear on their own.
Doesn't matter, right?
The mystery's solved,
so it's all good.
It was just a lucky guess.
I gotta say, Gao's
got great instincts.
Tasuku, the terms
of your suspension‐‐
I'm not to conduct
police business.
I promise it won't happen again.
(chuckles)
Well, that was fun
and totally unexpected.
The Boy Wonder Cop
was riveting,
but there are a few
other Buddyfighters
I have my eye on.
Let's initiate Phase Two.
I'm curious to see how
many of them have potential
for Disaster Force.
♪
By the end of the day,
we'll have our new fighter.
What should we do with
the escaped special rare?
I'll leave that to you.
I won't disappoint you.
I have just the thing.
Activate Disaster Force.
Azi Dahaka!
(whirring)
(swooshing)
No, no!
Ah!
What's that?
Can we get
earthquakes at sea?
No, I think we hit something.
What could we
possibly have run into?
Icebergs don't simply appear.
Look, bro!
♪
Doh, if we collide
with one of those,
everyone will know
I can't swim good.
Come on, Daddy, we have to
try and get to the lifeboats!
I've got it, let's get
ourselves to the lifeboats!
(shouting)
♪
There isn't enough time to
lower the boats before impact.
I wouldn't do that.
Disobeying a direct order
will have severe consequences.
Huh?
Let's go to work, Jack.
♪
(roaring)
Tasuku, stop!
The use of Future Force
hasn't been authorized.
Hurry, there isn't much time.
Buddy Skill on.
♪
When will you get it?
This power exists
to help people.
Ah!
♪
Capture complete.
Now that you have the
monster under control,
what are you
gonna do with it?
It's been sentenced
for termination.
No matter how
valuable a card is,
if it doesn't obey
orders, it's useless.
You can't do that.
Yeah, stop!
So what if Axia is
extremely annoying
and a dragon I'd secretly
like to breathe fire on?
He's definitely
right about one thing.
All monsters want to
choose their own buddies.
Even me, I chose Gao,
and I'm glad I did.
At first, I thought
he was just a wimp
who ran away from fights.
Now, I'd risk
my life for him.
I'm proud to
fight beside him.
Fine, if it means
so much to you.
But let's see what you're
willing to do for it.
(grunting)
‐I'm coming!
‐Uh‐oh.
I don't have my drill!
So that's what Father meant
by look before you leap.
Gao, be careful!
Watch the current, bro!
‐Ah!
‐Hang on!
I'm warning you!
Time to release
the Future Force!
♪
Okay, Jackknife,
unfold first move.
♪
Become one with the lightning
and harness your
awesome power!
Reveal Jackknife Thunderstorm!
Tasuku's using that awesome
real‐world force again.
Now that's what
I'm talkin' about.
♪
I'd give anything
for Jackknife's power.
Dragonblade, Dragobrave!
♪
(grunting)
Down on the icebergs, Jack!
Thunder Rage!
(zapping)
♪
I cast!
We need maximum power
to save these people.
Let's combine our
energies to become one.
Impact!
♪
Dragonic Punisher!
(whooshing)
♪
That's what I call power, man.
Amazing.
(whooshing)
Huh?
Uh‐oh, it's him again.
Uh‐huh.
He's probably behind this.
So that's the Future
Force, and right on cue.
Just one question
remains, however.
Is it stronger than
my Disaster Force?
How can I ever repay you?
‐You're a hero!
‐Let go of me!
Haven't you ever heard
of personal space?
I'm a hugger, don't
pretend to be so modest.
You're the strongest
ever, my Buddy.
Get off of me!
You're not seriously
talking about Drum, are you?
Who else, I never believed
I'd ever find my Buddy.
Uh, reality check,
we're both monsters.
Whatever, there's
nothing I like more
than breaking the rules.
Cut it out!
Hmm.
Listen to me, if you
really want to pay me back,
then help out Gao for me.
I'll do anything
for you, Drum!
What are you talking about?
Where are you gonna be?
About that, I need
to take a little trip.
Huh?
The way things are right now,
I just can't call
myself your Buddy.
Are you kidding me?
You still won't accept
me as your Buddy?
No, you've got it backwards.
I'm the one who's
not worthy of you.
Jack reminded me.
I need to get some
strong abilities like him
so I can protect you.
What's wrong with the way
things are right now?
We just won the Cup.
As the Mighty
Sun Fighter says,
"There comes a time when
a dragon must fight alone,"
or something like that.
Please don't go!
See you soon, kid.
Axia, take care of him.
♪
Drum, wait!
Where are you going?
Drum!
Hello there, I'm Paruko,
here to guide you through
the world of Buddyfight.
Did you see that way cool
Buddyfight party on the ship?
The prize was gonna be
a special rare card.
For those who don't know,
the order of Buddyfight
cards goes common, uncommon,
then rare, double rare,
triple rare, and special rare.
But, you know, even
cards that aren't rare
are super important to
your supply in a Buddyfight.
Every card is precious.
Can you open a
Buddy rare card?
What do you think?
♪
Next time, I go to Dungeon
World for some training.
Meanwhile, the gang meets
a mysterious Buddyfighter
at the Castle Store, and
things get a little weird.
Next episode,
"Drum's Heroic Adventure!"