♪
Do you have what it
takes to Buddyfight?
Choose your favorite world
and use special cards
to summon its powerful
monsters into reality.
Challenge other fighters and
buddy call your toughest ally
to fight by your side.
Get ready to
raise the flag!
Impact Roaring Slash!
Gargantua Punisher!
Oh, this isn't good!
(roaring)
♪
Game over.
Winner is Gao Mikado.
Oh, yeah!
That's how you
take back control.
Even cards that usually
dominate against normal decks
are useless against
the awesome power
of the Darkness
Dragon World.
The enemy cannot benefit from
their unique fighting style,
which prevents them from
achieving their full potential.
Observe your opponent,
predict their next move,
then turn the
tables on them.
Baku, the power of Darkness
Dragon World will guide you
as it shatters the
dreams of the defeated.
Once reunited,
we will celebrate
our victory together.
♪
Hello, everyone.
Thank you all so much
for coming here today.
As a major fan,
and a fighter,
I'm glad we
can come together
to raise the flag and
share our strengths.
Clearly, you
love the game.
That's why you're sponsoring
the Gaen Cup tournament,
but for someone who can
basically do anything he wants,
why Buddyfighting?
Well, it's a great way to
have fun and make friends.
And why did you make the
tournament kids only?
All over the world, terrible
tragedies are happening,
one after the other.
We need change and empowering
young people is the key.
I believe that we need to start
giving kids a stronger voice.
As they say, children
are our future.
Quite inspiring.
Now, how will the participating
Buddyfighters be selected?
As this is the
inaugural cup,
there's been very little time
for me and my staff to prepare.
We chose this
year's eight teams
based on past experience
and achievements.
I've already sent
out official invitations
to the players we want
highlighting our event.
Lucky for them.
I can hardly wait.
Today, we've been fortunate to
have, as our guest, Kyoya Gaen.
Head of the Gaen
Financial Group.
Thank you so
much for coming!
Give me a break.
I need a barf bag.
Those Disaster guys
are majorly bad news.
And Mr. Talk Show's the
mastermind of it all,
and no one's
gonna believe us.
It's just not fair.
Hmm?
You listening, kid?
♪
Do you think Gao is
gonna enter the tournament?
The invitation
says that each team
has to have three
Buddyfighters to enter.
If he does, he'll need
two more players, bro.
Thing is, knowing how
Gao deals with things,
he probably doesn't want anyone
else to be involved in this.
Still, I don't think
he really has a choice
if he wants to find out
where they took Tasuku.
♪
He sure got this place
rebuilt pretty fast.
Never underestimate the power
of the Gaen Financial Group.
Everything goes according
to our young master's wishes.
Why did you call this
urgent meeting, master?
I can tell you.
It's about the Gaen Cup.
Maybe you can tell us
why you're sponsoring
such a thing in
the first place.
♪
It's an experiment.
What experiment?
It would take too long
to explain it now,
but don't you worry.
It's all going to
be taken care of.
Mwah!
♪
I don't trust
anything that you say.
Oh, please don't
pout, Rouga.
Anyway, the reason that
we asked you all here today
is to announce which of
you will be participating
in the Gaen Cup.
We will be entering two teams
from Disaster in the tournament,
and they are as follows.
Team One: Sofia Sakharov...
Good.
Rouga Aragami,
and Mr. Purgatory
Knight makes three!
What did you
just call him?
You heard right.
Do you really expect me to work
with a guy dressed like that?
That armor is
his Core gadget.
Let's see your face.
♪
Get back here!
Show me some respect!
Calm down, no need
to make a big scene.
If I'm not on
the first team,
I hope that you've at least
included me on the second one.
There's no way I'm gonna
be on a team with you again.
Now, now, my friends.
Be nice because you're
competing side by side again
in the second group and
we're happy to announce
that Terumi will
be the third member!
What?
You mean I have to
team up with her too?
Yeah, like
you're a prize.
This is Master
Kyoya's decision.
Huh?
♪
Okay, then.
If Master wants
me to continue
lending my support
to this useless girl,
then I guess
I have no choice.
♪
The power your possess
can make a difference.
Change things
for the better.
So, what do you say?
Do we have
an agreement?
♪
So, why don't you throw
away that dark power
and let yourself be free?
I can't.
I have a power that
will help save the world.
Excuse me, what
are you mumbling about?
Trade him out!
I can't even stand
sitting with him!
(shrieks)
I can relate.
Listen here!
I'm twice the Buddyfighter
you'll ever be!
Please, I'll
do anything.
Don't kid yourself.
Just because you
weren't punished
for messing up
the other day,
doesn't mean
you're all that.
If you have a problem
cooperating with me,
then why don't you do us
all a favor and leave now?
(growls)
(yells)
♪
She pushed me,
you're all witnesses!
I say we band together
and kick her out of Disaster!
No one really
cares what you think.
Oh.
Fine, but we
still need to find
a third member
for my team,
and the only
one left is...
Ah!
Hmm.
Morning you two.
How's it going?
Hey, sorry, we're late!
Just a guess, but you still
haven't made a decision,
have you, bro?
About what?
The Gaen Cup, obviously.
He even talks
about it in his sleep.
Well, at least,
I don't snore!
Nice of you to
finally show up.
I've been waiting to see
if you wanted to
team up for the tournament.
We both want to uncover
the mystery of Disaster.
We need to get rid of
these Dark Core deck cases
and expose them for
the criminals they are.
Sounds good, but it
could all be a trap.
Everything in life has
an element of danger,
but it's nothing
we can't handle together.
Besides, if we
don't enter a team,
we'll never know what
happened to Tasuku, will we?
Could you
live with that?
So, this is where
all y'all are.
I thought maybe you'd be off
training to get yourself ready.
You are gonna
compete, aren't you?
I mean, you have to.
♪
I cast Evil Crusher,
Steel Dragon Barrage!
(explosion)
♪
(grunting)
You're not giving
up so easily.
No.
I am not, Kem.
That's what
I like to hear!
Genma.
Yeah, what is it?
We've received an invitation
to the Gaen Cup.
It was addressed
to the Seifukai.
♪
Hmm.
Is this a bad time?
♪
Oh, it's you.
(yawns)
To what do I
owe the pleasure?
We just received this rather
intriguing invitation
addressed to
Sengoku Academy.
I'm sure it's nothing
to get too excited about.
What are you going
to do about the Gaen Cup?
I don't know.
You're aware that
I'm still busy
helping out
Mr. Takihara, right?
♪
(phone vibrating)
Hang on a mo.
♪
This sounds fun.
You don't want our help cause
you think it'll be dangerous?
♪
But I'm a break‐dancing demon.
I bring the danger.
We weren't just gonna
leave you hanging, yo!
I was talking, Tets.
Seriously, though, you guys
are gonna need some backup.
I think I get it.
So in exchange for helping
us expose disaster,
you want us to
include him on our team.
♪
Hmm.
Huh, when you put it that way,
it sounds even better!
You still need one more
Buddyfighter, am I right?
Come on, me and A‐dog
would totally rock it!
It's nothing personal,
but I've never believed
you were that interested in
becoming a champion fighter.
Huh?
What are you saying?
I heard you won
that Aibo dance contest.
Yep, you're
100% correct, yo.
All that practicing
with Asmodai paid off,
but what's that got to do
with me being on your team?
You're a cool guy, but maybe
it's time to face facts.
I must've heard you wrong.
I got to stop
cranking up my speakers.
Will someone please
tell me what's going on?
Listen, Tets, you
should quit Buddyfighting
and concentrate
on your dancing.
What?
At least, that's what Zanya
thinks you should do.
I hate to say it, but your
buddy's got it right.
Music, that's
your strong suit.
And that's the reason you
should be devoting yourself
entirely to dancing.
No way, forget that, yo!
Yeah, I do like bustin' a move,
but I can't give up Buddyfights.
I never see you put half as
much dedication and practice
into improving your game
as you put into your routines.
Then I challenge you.
Why don't we settle
this thing with a match?
And after I beat you, I'll make
you take back those harsh words.
Hmm!
He's riled up.
I'd like to say that it
would be a waste of time,
but I don't think it
would make any difference.
♪
It's him.
(laughing)
So pathetic.
(crying)
I wonder what he's doing.
♪
Who gets first turn?
You go ahead
if you wanna, yo.
That was your last mistake.
Charge and draw.
I call to the center,
Electron Ninja, Shiden.
I use Server Analyze
and draw two more cards.
Attack the fighter!
(grunts)
‐Final Phase!
‐Huh?
I pay one gauge and set
Super Lethal Formation!
I've never even
heard of that one.
What does it do?
♪
Set.
Well, he puts one Secret
Sword card in the soul,
just like in
Lethal Formation.
But this card
increases the power
and the defense of all the
ninjas in the field by 1,000.
End of move.
Since his opponent's
using Magic World,
it's obviously going to be
Secret Sword Star Crusher.
I call Demon Realm Warrior,
Zepar, to the left.
Demon Realm Death Metal,
Valefar, to the right.
And Street Racer, Eligos,
to the center, yo!
Bring it, Valefar!
Go and attack Shiden!
Oh, yeah, music is my life!
♪
Show's over!
Eligos, Zepar, take
out Zanya right now!
Hey there, ninja, do you
need a ride to Loserville?
Courtside Blaster!
(grunts)
End of move.
Star Crusher won't
let him use spell cards,
so all he can do is
line up the 72 pillars
and repeat frontal attacks.
You must know that players
who use Magic World
need to have a lot of technique
and skill to be effective,
but I see you still haven't
learned to use it properly
and that's because
you're not dedicated
to doing what
it takes to win.
(laughing)
This guy's got
some nerve, huh?
Hey, why are you laughing?
You're killing my vibe!
Some people have to
learn the hard way.
Draw!
Charge and draw!
♪
I cast Clear Serenity!
I call to the center
Wanderer, the Gold.
He's totally cool.
He can attack
all the monsters
in the playing area
at the same time.
♪
In bloom all year round,
Cherry Blossom Storm!
(all groaning)
♪
(grunting)
(yells)
Huh?
Remote Punishment!
♪
(groaning)
End of move.
Z's got six life points left.
With Super
Lethal Formation,
Wanderer, the Gold,
can get 6,000 defense.
There's no way he's
gonna get through that.
That Katana World user.
He's a pretty
strong fighter.
This is brutal.
Tetsuya needs a hug.
Doesn't help that he
can't use spell cards.
Huh?
Secret Sword Star Crusher.
The one that activates
when a spell card's used?
Yeah, you know.
The impact card that
nullifies the spell
and also causes
three damage points.
It looks like
it's all over
unless he can somehow
defeat Wanderer, the Gold.
Without any spells,
Tetsuya's gonna bomb
harder than at his
first rap battle.
Draw!
Charge and draw!
♪
If I wanna win, I'm gonna have
to use a spell here, yo!
So I cast Great Spell
Devil's Rock and Roll.
(growling)
But he can't do that.
I've read about that card.
If there are 72 pillars in the
top five cards in his deck,
he can call three
of them if he wants.
I call Eligos to the right.
Valefar to the left,
and I buddy call
the one and only demon‐lord
Asmodai to the center, yo!
Alright, way to
figure it out!
Now, time to dance!
I discard one card.
The rest is up to you.
(grunting)
Back drop!
(screams)
I don't get it.
How'd he know that Zanya
didn't set Star Crusher?
Break it down!
Street Racer Eligos,
you got the floor.
Yo, yo, yo, yo!
I cast Art of
Body Replacement!
Your turn, go
get him, Valefar!
You can't stop the beat, yo!
I'll say one thing, he does seem
to be having fun out there.
Where are your
moves now, huh?
That's my cue
to step it up.
Asmodai, attack the fighter!
One, two.
One, two, three, four!
(grunts)
Devilish drop kick!
♪
End of move.
What's happening?
(grunts)
Your move.
Draw.
Charge and draw.
I cast Clear Serenity.
No big deal.
I can pull off that
kind of stuff too.
Huh?
I equip Ninja
Blade Kurogachi!
I buddy call to the right,
Nanomachine Ninja Tsukikage!
Nin!
Right, Tsukikage,
attack Asmodai!
Nin!
(grunts)
♪
(yelling)
End of move.
How do you escape
that with four life?
Draw!
Charge and draw!
I call to the center, Demon
Realm Warrior Zepar!
Wait, he has three monsters!
Yeah, and if
this attack hits.
Hang on, then
Tetsuya will win.
♪
Hey, Eligos, time to chase
the fighter out of here!
Alright, I'm gonna
ride like the wind!
I cast.
I pay four gauge.
And I cast the Secret Arts
Dance of the Guardian Sword!
Awesome!
Big Z is in the zone!
That's another card
that can destroy
all of an opponent's monsters.
Total annihilation again!
Now can you see how much
more dedicated I am?
Oh, the fight
isn't over yet, though.
I cast.
Key of Solomon, First Volume,
and I'll cast again.
Great Spell
Saturday Night!
Devil Fever!
‐Yeah!
Woo, Saturday
Night Devil Fever!
‐Huh?
‐I'll get rid of a card,
and activate
Asmodai's mad skill.
Dangerous backdrop,
freestyle!
Z doesn't have any
cards left in his hand.
Everyone, attack the
fighter together now.
Topside Blaster!
(grunts)
(grunting)
No fair!
Can I have
this dance?
He did it!
A monster with
over 5,000 power.
That's what you get when you
attack with Demon Lord Asmodai.
Hey, where'd he go?
You've fallen
right into my trap.
I pay three gauge and activate
Super Lethal Formation.
Secret Sword Comet!
Oh, dang.
(grunts)
(screaming)
♪
Game over.
Winner: Zanya Kisaragi.
You're right, I'm not working
hard enough on my game.
I was wrong.
Using that spell
card when you did
proves you're
a strong player.
For realsies?
Magic World really doesn't
have many monsters like me
that have over
5,000 power.
I'm really surprised that you
put the Comet card in the soul.
Everyone at the Academy knows
what great friends you two are.
So I figured that when
it came down to it,
Tetsuya would want to
attack with his buddy,
and as usual,
my hunch was right.
We were just
outmatched this time.
(groans)
That's not true.
Huh?
To be honest, if
Asmodai wasn't called
when you used Great Spell
Saturday Night Devil Fever,
then I would have
been the one to lose.
Please forgive me, and the bad
things that I said about you.
No prob!
And the next time we fight,
we'll do it as teammates.
Sure, sounds like a plan.
♪
So, whatcha gonna do, Gao?
(sighs)
Come on, stop being
such a buzz kill.
Asmodai said he'd take care of
all the dangerous stuff, right?
So, there's nothing
to worry about.
Now quit moping around over
things you can't control.
It's driving
everyone crazy.
Get your head
in the game, kid.
We're entering
the Gaen Cup,
but we got to do it with one
super important goal in mind.
What kind of goal are
you talking about, man?
To have fun
Buddyfighting.
♪
Then it's decided?
That means Team Balle
du Soleil is back again.
If you guys are
okay with the name.
I look forward to
working with you.
Me too.
You've got it
going on, yo.
You're two of the best
players in the school.
I can't believe
this is my life,
but if I'm gonna be
fighting beside you,
I want in on
all the perks.
Here, Baku!
Wait, let me guess.
You want me to
build you a new deck.
The kind that will match your
fighting skill perfectly.
You're reading my mind, yo.
Fun is for silly people
who have time to waste.
I need to fight
how Master wants me to.
That's my Buddyfighting style.
Oh, so now you
want to be on my team?
Why the sudden
change of heart?
No reason.
That's fine,
I don't care anyways.
But sadly, you're no longer
allowed to compete in the cup.
What? Well, why not?
Master Kyoya's decision.
It was something
about how
you're no longer
a member of Disaster.
Sorry.
♪
No, I have to
go talk to him!
♪
(screams)
Personally, I don't think
that'd be a good idea.
(door clangs shut)
It's time for...
Tasuku and Gao's...
‐Card of the day!
Today we're gonna talk to
you about a really cool card
called Horn of Demise,
Gjallarhorn.
It's a spell card that lets you
move Great Spell Fimbullwinter
from your deck to your hand.
Yeah, and if the
person using the card
is in elementary school,
they can also add Great Spell
Ragnarok to their hand
at the same time.
Unfortunately for me,
I'm not eligible anymore.
I am, man,
I can still use it!
So, what do you think, guys?
You think you can
open up one of these?
You'll never
know until you try!
♪
Next time,
the Gaen Cup begins
and we're up first
against Team Goddess.
Zanya predicts an easy victory
before he steps onto the stage,
but he isn't expecting
what happens next.
Next episode,
"The Gaen Cup Begins!"
Join us for
a Buddyfight!