♪
Get ready for a
cool new card game
that connects to
a parallel universe.
Special cards
act as portals,
bringing
monsters to Earth
to become
buddies with humans.
And through
friendship and courage,
help them take on
fight challenges.
It's called
Buddyfight.
♪
I'm actually glad.
Why is that?
To be honest,
I can't remember
the last time I was
challenged to a fight
outside of work.
Well then, are we gonna
get started or what?
Not so fast, Gao.
Huh?
Mr. Natsuke?
You're all supposed
to be in your classrooms.
Even you, Mr. Ryuenji.
You're right.
I should get back
before next period.
We'll have to
do this later.
Aw.
even though Tasuku works
for the buddy card office,
he manages to do double duty
as a grade seven student.
What about the fight, huh?
(crowd grumbling)
I get why the
kids are bummed.
What do you say
we reschedule the match
for after school?
I'll even authorize you
to use the amphitheater,
the pride of Aibo Academy.
Wow, thank you,
Mr. Neginoyama.
Did you hear that?
The battle's on after all
and our lovable, but eccentric
Buddyfight history teacher,
Mr. Neginoyama,
will let them use
our world famous
fighting stage!
Hah.
♪
(chuckle)
Hmm.
Hmm, hmm, hmm.
(sizzling)
Excuse me, are you Drum?
Quit calling me Drum.
My title is
Son of Drum Bunker Dragon,
Fang Slade Terrestrial
the Thirteenth.
What, should I etch it
in stone for you humans?
Just how long
are you planning
to stay looking like that?
Huh?
Every monster
from an alien world
knows that they have
to change their appearance
so they don't scare
humans while on Earth.
Other than during
buddyfights, of course.
I am rather terrifying.
And if those are the rules.
(wind swirling)
Aw.
So, is this all right?
Great.
Wait a sec.
Jack didn't have to
change the way he looks.
That's 'cause everybody knows
Jack is Tasuku Ryuenji's buddy,
but no one knows
who you are.
(growling)
So, Gao, do you think
you can beat Tasuku?
Don't know‐‐I've never
had to build a deck before.
‐Huh?
And you still challenged
Tasuku to a Buddyfight?
What did I get myself
into with this guy?
Father said to choose a
human who is unconventional,
but this is ridiculous.
Ha ha, don't sweat it.
I'm sure I can
figure it out.
Gao versus Tasuku!
♪
Man, I'm starving.
Before we eat, I've
got to check something.
(gurgling)
Was that your
stomach or mine?
Stomach, who cares?
We've got to
get back inside.
I'm hungry.
I can't explain now,
but if you want to eat,
we've got to get out of here.
♪
Going somewhere?
Huh?
Don't tell me you
forgot our bet already.
What's on the menu today?
Grrrrr.
Hmm.
Well, if you insist.
So, what is it?
Oh, no, why
today of all days?
Granny made me her
delicious octopus dumplings!
Sure beats eating
northby legs back home.
Hey!
Who said you could eat any?
Don't be so stingy.
We're buddies, aren't we?
Thanks for the eats.
Gaaa!
I don't believe it!
How could you,
I didn't get a single one!
(grumbling)
Uh, I don't feel good.
So hungry,
not gonna make it.
Uh?
Here, you can
have some of mine.
Are you serious?
Gee, thanks Kuguru.
There is a catch, though.
I have a favor
to ask you.
What kind of favor?
These look good.
You want to lose that‐‐
For your Buddyfight
with Tasuku,
I want you to let Baku
build a deck for you.
You got that?
‐Huh?
You must be
totally delusional.
He's a rookie.
There's no way he
could master my deck.
Well, we won't know
till I try, now will we?
‐Hey, Baku?
‐Hmm?
Remember just the other day...
♪
I see you‐‐when this
hose connects here,
the fuel line
feeds through the‐‐
Hey, I got it.
Ah.
I saw you practicing
for your mechanics test
on Mr. Natsuke's car.
What do you
think would happen
if he were to
find out about it?
I bet you'd get suspended.
Maybe even expelled.
Okay, I'll do it.
Cool!
Drum Bunker Dragon, is it?
Offensive and defensive
powers are both high,
5,000 each.
It also has a super rare
ability called soul guard,
allowing it
to remain standing
even if destroyed,
but just once,
a seriously awesome card.
Finally, someone who gets me.
Hmm, buddy with him then.
At least he understands me.
Hmm, chill out and
leave everything to me.
Baku, I just
have one request.
It's a favor, actually.
What now?
I want you to build a deck
that will allow me
to fight as well.
Hmm?
♪
Fighting is the
great privilege
of we Armor Dragons.
So you can just stay back
in your safe little corner
like a typical dragon knight.
No way, I'm not gonna just
stand around in the background
shouting instructions
the whole time.
You got that?
I want to be out there
on the battlefield,
shoulder to shoulder
with you guys.
Mmmm.
♪
Then you're in luck,
'cause players
are allowed to fight.
That's probably one
of the best things
about Buddyfight.
‐Hmm?
But to do it, you're
gonna need an item card
like this one.
Just know that by using it,
you'll weaken your
defensive position.
I don't care,
add it to the deck.
♪
Now this one
is a must have.
Here we are at Aibo
Academy's fighting stage
about to witness a Buddyfight
with none other than
our very own boy wonder
and member of
the Buddycard office,
Tasuku Ryuenji!
Look at the
intensity in his eyes.
Oh, those eyes, so dreamy.
We love you, Tasuku!
His opponent is sixth
grader, Gao Mikado,
a total novice
who didn't even start
buddyfighting
till this year.
And in this reporter's
humble opinion,
has no business challenging
a seasoned pro like Tasuku.
♪
Good luck, Gao!
Huh, Hana?
Get that buddy police guy.
Thanks, sis!
‐Hey, Gao?
‐Huh?
There'll be a lot
of people out there
watching us today,
but don't let it
get to you, okay?
Thanks, but no need
to worry about me,
I've got a few tricks
up my sleeve.
Good luck out there.
All right, good luck
to you as well.
Hah.
Gather dragon army.
Dragonic Force, Luminize!
'Kay, now it's my turn.
Ha, release Baku's super
explosive dragon deck.
Dragon Blast Fury, Luminize!
You're kidding me.
(giggling)
His core gadget's a belt?
Huh, this guy's totally
embarrassing himself.
You're super cool,
big brother!
I really like your belt!
It suits you perfectly!
It even looks like the sun!
Huh?
The sun?
Ha.
‐Now I can't lose.
‐Huh?
Eclipsing the
darkness with flames,
and brightening the hearts
of the mistreated.
Aah!
There he goes!
The Mighty Sun
Fighter is here!
Now, let's get
this thing started.
It appears both
competitors are ready.
So the match
can finally begin.
Buddy...
Fight!
(cheering)
‐Time to raise the flag!
Dragon World!
Raahhhr!
Grrrr!
♪
Rahhhr!
Tasuku is up first.
Charge and draw.
♪
I call to the center,
Jamadhar Dragon!
Ah!
♪
Rahrr!
Jamadhar,
you know what to do.
With pleasure.
Aargh.
♪
End of move.
What a play!
Gao's already suffered
two damage points.
Another eight points
and Gao's life count
will drop to zero
and he'll lose the match.
Your move.
Draw.
Charge and draw!
I'm coming for you, Tasuku.
Thousand Rapier
Dragon to the right.
And Systemic Dagger
Dragon to the left.
♪
Rahhr!
Oh, wow, he's calling
two monsters at once!
Big whoop, he's
still gonna lose.
Clearly you know nothing
about the size rule.
If the total size
counts three or less,
you can call as many
monsters in one hand
as you want.
At least I don't have
a kitten on my shirt!
It's a tiger,
not a kitten.
Gao, attack Tasuku!
Then send your
dragons to get Noboru!
He can't do that.
He can't attack
when there's a monster
occupying his center area.
Oh, oh?
And with this one card, I
cast Dragonblade, Dragobrave.
♪
Aaaaahhaaa!
It's a triple
offensive maneuver.
Is that good?
Yes, it's the
strongest formation.
Only a doofus would
move into position.
Now he has no defense.
I guess he was serious
about fighting after all.
Thousand Rapier,
move to attack Jamadhar!
Clear the area
in front of Tasuku!
Right.
♪
In vino veritas!
(laughing)
Systemic dagger,
let's attack together.
You got it.
Yah!
♪
Haaaaa!
(smashing)
End of move.
Go, Gao!
He struck five damage
points on his first turn?
Your move.
Come on, Jack, we've got
some catching up to do.
This'll be tougher
than I first thought.
♪
Charge and draw.
To the center area,
I call Latale Shield Dragon!
Raarr!
I cast Dragonic Charge.
♪
And now, Dragonic Shoot!
Ah!
Ugh, Systemic Dagger!
Up next, Dragon Flame.
♪
Oh, no, Thousand Rapier!
And now for...
Dragon Crush.
♪
My Dragobrave!
Annihilated.
Out skilled and out classed,
with a flurry of
spell card assaults,
Tasuku's wiped out
everything in Gao's field.
One more,
thanks to your
previous attack.
Uuhhh!
Dragonic Grimoire!
He was waiting
for this chance
to use his super
powerful spell card
that can only be cast
when your life points
drop to five or less.
The only thing left
for Gao to do is lose.
Okay, Jack,
it's up to you.
I buddy call
to the right area‐‐
Huh?
♪
Rar!
(growling)
By choosing to call
his buddy into play,
Tasuku gains one life point.
What brilliant
strategizing,
what a move!
Yeah, yeah.
Give 'em what they
came to see, Jack.
Let's win this.
(metal clanking)
‐Here it comes.
‐Yeah.
♪
Latale.
Aargh!
End of move.
Check it out, everyone,
Gao has only three
life points left!
Will he play
the super duper rare card
that no one else in the world
has but Tasuku Ryuenji?
Is it time for
the Gargantua Punisher?
Hang on a sec,
is Gao gonna lose?
No, he's still in the game.
Ah?
There are three
conditions that must be met
before a player can use
Gargantua Punisher.
First, the opposing
player must have
four or fewer life points.
Second, there
can't be a monster
holding either
player's center area.
And third‐‐
A player must have a
gauge of four or more
before they can use it.
And right now, Tasuku
is only at gauge three.
Yeah, but after
the next turn?
(sighing)
Uh.
Your move.
Draw.
Charge and draw!
'Kay, look
alive there, buddy,
you're up next.
And here I thought
you'd forgotten about me.
Put me in the center
to protect you.
Huh?
I wonder if he'll use
Drum Bunker Dragon?
Well, he should.
Thing is, he's not
playing him right away
so he's likely only
got size two monsters.
Well then, he should call
Drum to the center area.
With his soul guard ability,
he'll be able to
fend off two attacks.
Yeah, let's see
if he remembers.
Come on, what's the matter?
Easy, Drum, what we should
be thinking about now
is not how to avoid losing,
but how we're gonna win.
Whatever, just put me
in the center and hurry!
They have six
life points remaining
to our measly three.
♪
Wha, ha.
Buddy call.
Huh?
(smashing)
Aaarrgh!
Drum, go to the right!
Huh, the right?
Buddy gift, which
means one life point gain.
You just lost
us the game, bozo.
There it is, I knew
he'd make a big mistake.
Hmm, but why didn't he
put him in the center?
(sighing)
I'm counting
on you, partner.
Let's win this!
What do you mean partner?
I don't want to be
your buddy anymore.
Okay, now attack
Latale Shield.
Are we speaking
the same language?
Mmmmm, go Drum, attack!
♪
Grrrrrr!
End of move.
Tasuku is already at
an overwhelming advantage.
And for some
reason in his turn,
Gao didn't call Drum Bunker
Dragon to the center area.
In my opinion,
this match is pretty much
a done deal.
Your move.
You saw right through me.
Somehow you figured
out that I don't have
any size one monsters or
item cards left in my hand.
But I do have one
interesting card left.
Huh?
♪
Equip Dragon Blade,
Dragofearless.
♪
Huh, what's he got there?
He's got an offensive power
of 3,000/2 fright points.
What does that mean?
Is Gao gonna lose?
Not necessarily.
Hmm.
I'd love to stick around
and keep battling you,
but I should get going.
So it's time to
end this thing, Gao.
♪
Arrgh!
Go!
Is this the end
for Gao Mikado?
Not yet.
♪
Green Dragon Shield.
I don't believe it!
That card can only be used
when there's no monster
in his center area!
Plus Gao gains
one life point.
Well played, Gao.
End of move.
He survived that turn,
but he's only
got three life points
to Tasuku's six.
The most damage his
size one monsters can do
is just two points.
So he can only inflict five
damage points at the most?
I wonder what
Tasuku is gonna do
in his next turn?
♪
Maybe Gargantua Punisher.
Your move.
You got lucky
back there, kid.
I disagree‐‐besides,
when am I gonna start
getting some
cred for my brains
instead of always
being called lucky?
Well, what are you
gonna do now, brainiac?
Huh, the way I see it,
there's only one way
we're gonna beat Tasuku,
using Dragobrave
one more time.
Wait a sec.
Kuguru, what's the
most powerful item card
in terms of striking points?
Dragonblade, Dragobrave.
Its attack power is 5,000
and it causes
three damage points.
Sweet, I'll put four
of those into the deck.
Use them if you get
into any trouble.
Hah.
He has three
Dragobraves left.
Hope he remembers them.
Draw.
Time to charge, eh?
Just 'cause
you used Dragobrave
doesn't guarantee
you the win.
Tasuku's only holding
size two monsters
and offensive spell
cards in his hand.
And how do you know that?
If he doesn't, then
there's no chance I can win.
The only way
I'm gonna defeat him
is for me to
believe in myself
and make the draw.
Kid's not bad.
I know.
Okay, here goes nothing.
Uh, aaah, ahh!
‐Draw it.
‐Come on.
You're kidding.
Ha!
Cast Dragonblade,
Dragobrave!
♪
No way, he drew it!
All right, Drum,
you go first.
Okay.
♪
Crash, drill that bunker!
Aaaah!
♪
Game over.
Winner is Gao Mikado.
Huh, thank you,
thank you very much.
(cheering)
(screaming)
For the first time in
my life, I'm speechless.
In a stunning upset,
buddy police
Tasuku Ryuenjii has lost.
Super novice Gao Mikado has
actually beaten my Tasuku!
Hah, he just lucked out
with drawing the
right cards is all.
It's just a game
of chance, you see.
If you seriously
believe that, bro,
then you're never gonna
win a match against Gao.
Yeah, right.
Baku!
‐Huh?
‐Hmm?
Thanks a lot, huh.
Your Dragonblast
Fury deck rocked!
I could have never
built a deck like that.
You, my friend,
are a total genius.
Hey, thanks, but I
think your playing skills
had more to do with it.
Huh?
That was a pretty
fun match, Gao.
Got to say, you had
some solid tactics.
♪
You're no officially my
biggest Buddyfight rival.
Uh?
I'd like you to
have this card.
But that's
Gargantua Punisher.
‐Huh?
(murmuring)
Use it well.
As you know,
it's a unique card.
And I'd really like
to see you master it.
Ahh.
♪
Hmm.
The special rare Gargantua
Punisher card is all yours.
Ah, Gargantua Punisher's
really mine?
Seriously?
♪
Hello there, I'm
Paruko, here to guide you
through the world
of Buddyfight.
Tasuku Ryuenji catches
criminals who use buddies
for very bad things.
He may only be
in the seventh grade,
but he's definitely
the number one
best buddyfighter
in the whole world!
So the big question is
how the great master Tasuku
lost to a newbie like Gao?
You know, folks, I think Gao
must have cheated or something
otherwise there's no way
he could have won.
Can you open a buddy rare card?
What do you think?
♪
Next episode, Gao tries to find
a tuner, or training partner,
that he can get along with.
He settles on
Tetsuya Kurodake,
and wait 'till
you see who his buddy
from the magic world is.
Dancing with a Demon
on the next Buddyfight.