♪
Get ready for a
cool new card game
that connects to
a parallel universe!
Special cards
act as portals
bringing monsters to Earth
to become buddies with humans,
and through
friendship and courage,
help them take
on fight challenges.
It's called Buddyfight!
Ah.
Huh?
(yelling)
♪
He's at Sengoku Academy?
They took Kiri there?
‐It's that bad?
‐Yeah, bro.
How come?
I'm stumped.
Ah! That place
is too real!
Be easy, Tets,
it's all good.
What's the deal?
It sounds like this
school is pretty rough.
Please tell
us Gao, please?
I'll tell you
everything I know.
♪
Actually, the truth is
I really don't know anything.
(all yell)
What is wrong with you?
I don't like being
held in suspense!
Ha ha, you should
have seen your faces!
Lucky for you, I've uploaded
the video presentation
I did on Sengoku Academy
for history class!
Hit the lights!
♪
The school first opened during
Japan's Sengoku period.
It was a time of war,
so to remain undetected
from feuding lords,
the secret academy was built
deep in the mysterious mountains
of Chohakone.
Trained in all
forms of combat,
the students had just
one purpose: to win.
The school made its
own code of justice.
Whoever wins is right
and their motto is
"Swifter, higher, stronger."
They eat, sleep and breathe
every kind of martial arts,
but that's not all,
my riveted friends.
‐Huh?
Along with all
the other subjects,
they also had an excellent
Buddyfight training program,
but they were never
able to become champions.
Because time after time,
our very own Aibo Academy
has stood in their way.
Tired of being humiliated,
our determined rivals completely
changed their lesson plans
and now, everything
is decided by matches.
You got to be kidding me!
Sounds kinda intense.
Only the most competitive
Buddyfighters are accepted.
If someone looks at you the
wrong way, you Buddyfight.
If there's something
that you want,
you settle it
with a Buddyfight,
no matter what it is, where
or when, you must Buddyfight.
To help the students tap
into their natural instincts,
they supposedly
have wild animals
roaming freely
in the nearby forest.
It's like a Buddyfight
obsession over there.
So if you go, you better
be prepared for the worst.
We have to go,
Kiri could be in danger!
Then what are
we waiting for?
Hey, don't forget
to count me in too.
No can do.
The school is built ridiculously
far into the mountains, bro.
Even with Drum's nose, it's
risky to scope it out at night.
That's the truth.
Nighttime's dangerous.
Let's get some sleep and
walk it out in the morning.
(yawns)
Catching some Z's
sounds good to me.
I'm too awake!
You just got to hold on
a little bit longer, Kiri.
♪
Everyone came!
‐Of course!
‐Yeah!
I can't say I'm not
surprised you showed, Zanya.
I kinda owe Kiri for helping
me out at the ABC Cup.
You might have lost to Magatsu
without my stunt double.
Me.
It's sweet of you
to come, Kazane.
You don't even
really know Kiri.
No problem.
You've all been
so nice to me.
Besides, how could I
pass up visiting a school
where they let you
Buddyfight all the time?
Imagine facing off with
everyone in the school.
Playing until you're too
tired to stand anymore.
Plus, they've got tons of
cuddly animals to play with!
♪
If you ask me, it
sounds like a dream.
Did she even listen
to my presentation?
One dragon's dream is
another's nightmare.
You ill‐mannered mongrels, are
you actually insulting Kazane?
(shuddering)
So, how do we
roll with no wheels?
You know what I'm saying?
The fastest way would be
using our buddy skills.
But poor Gao
can't use his yet.
Really,
is that true?
(groans)
Come on, don't
sweat it, guys.
I think things
are looking up.
Huh?
What's going on?
Who turned out the lights?
Hey, is that‐‐
♪
And right on cue, Suzuha shows
up with her incredible sky home!
I heard Gao was worried
about his friends,
so I rushed
right over.
Sup, Suzuha,
thanks for coming!
♪
Looking good, Gao.
I hope that you find
your friend soon.
Thought you might like
to use my dressing blimp.
We'll be there faster
than you can count
my many pairs of shoes.
You are so awesome no matter
what other people say!
Thanks, I think.
So, where exactly will
we be going anyway?
To Sengoku Academy!
You really want me to
go to Sengoku Academy?
Yeah, sure.
You expect me to visit
that hive of barbarians?
It's a gathering
place for troublemakers
who are lucky to
bathe once a year!
Suzuha's down for the count
without taking a single blow!
♪
Thanks for
the cool ride!
Hope that you're
feeling better!
♪
My dearest Gao,
please be careful.
♪
You know how to pilot
this thing, A‐dog?
Talk about mad skills.
True that, is there
anything I can't do?
(yells)
What kinda motor
does this baby got?
Look, bro, it's
the air scoop control.
Can you hear me now?
Hello, hello,
are you there?
What's the matter?
There's bad
reception up here
and I can't
reach Takosuke!
Well, maybe he's
fallen asleep again.
Takosuke, can
you hear me?
Hey.
Want to have a Buddyfight
to kill some time?
I can't,
I'm afraid of‐‐
Heights.
You okay, Z?
(grunts)
Hang in there, Kiri.
We're coming.
♪
(snickering)
(nervous ribbiting)
Kemura's freaked
about the new kid
that he brought in yesterday.
Did you hear,
huh, did ya?
I hear everything.
Leave it be.
One thing we've
learned is that
no good ever comes
from dealing with him.
Don't tell me
you've forgotten.
Hmmph, we might
not have a choice.
Something to add, Kanahebi?
My buddy spotted a strange
airship headed straight for us.
It could be a problem.
This has Aragami
written all over it.
♪
Huh, you may be right.
We'll have to arrange a
welcome party for our guests.
What a complete eye sore!
(whistling)
♪
(yelling)
I don't believe it,
isn't that‐‐
Sky Ninja
Yamigarasu!
A monster from
Katana World.
Let's roll out
of here, people.
Stop bugging.
Part of being
a strong warrior
is staying cool
under pressure, you dig?
Sorry, A‐dog,
I'll try my best, yo.
But what if the birds
pop the blimp?
Then we're in
for a wild ride,
cause I don't have any
idea how to land this thing.
Should be fun.
(laughing)
You got a strange
sense of humor, yo.
♪
(screaming)
There's got to be parachutes
in here somewhere, bro!
What's this?
(shouts)
My bad!
Hey, I think we found
the parachutes.
These are dresses.
Maybe they're in here.
Girl overload!
I don't feel so good.
Well, if everybody's
pushing random buttons...
♪
(screaming)
(explosion)
That went better
than I expected.
Yeah, I'd give it
an eight out of ten.
Baku, are you okay?
Yeah, I think so.
Though you're a lot
heavier than you look.
(groans)
I meant that the
nicest possible way.
Thanks a lot for
the lift, Blade.
I'm happy to do it.
That was weird.
I thought a crash landing
would be worse than that.
What happened?
Did you throw down
some demon magic?
No, it wasn't me,
it was that guy.
Is everybody all
right in there?
It's Genma
and Duel Sieger!
(chuckling)
Rouga is up to his
old tricks again, I see.
So what brings you
to the middle of nowhere?
I like to get out here
as often as I can.
It's good to train in
the fresh mountain air.
Too many humans in
the city, am I right?
I wondered what
happened to Rouga.
I heard he transferred
to a different school.
It makes sense
he chose Sengoku.
A perfect fit for his true
nature and personality.
Yeah, good call, man.
A school that encourages
winning above all else,
and a student who will do
anything for victory.
Huh?
We're surrounded.
(gasps)
♪
You little kids lost?
Can't you read the signs?
You're trespassing on
Sengoku Academy turf!
Hey, I think these guys
are students at Sengoku.
This worked out great!
Now you can give us
a tour of your school.
If you want me to show you,
then you have to beat
me in a Buddyfight first.
♪
If there's something you want,
you settle it with Buddyfight.
I guess the rumors
about this place are true.
It's awesome!
‐Come on, Drum, we're up.
‐Right behind you!
♪
Gargantua Punisher!
(grunts)
It's settled, now
take us to your school.
I'd never take
you anywhere.
That's no way
to treat a guest.
♪
At Sen‐cad, we're taught that
the winner is always right
in any conflict
or challenge.
We're required to uphold
their wishes, no matter what.
As it should be, my name
is Shosetsu Kirisame.
And I welcome
you to Sengoku.
You're all from
Aibo Academy, correct?
Huh?
They're from Aibo?
Please follow me.
I'll take you where
you want to go.
Okay, thanks.
These are the dorms.
The students are
currently finishing up
their first three
hour training circuit.
No way!
If you think
that's tough,
wait until you
see what's next.
Have fun scrubbing
the latrines, pal!
This game is mine!
(laughing)
Let's go again!
You'll be doing my laundry
once I'm done beating you.
They use Buddyfights to decide
who completes which duties.
The guys you met
earlier lost already,
so they had to take the first
shift guarding the outside wall.
This isn't what I expected.
It's so serious.
Please, come in.
It's about time you
showed up, Mr. Mikado.
Huh?
How do you know my name?
(mocking laugh)
I saw your performance
at the ABC Cup.
You were very
impressive.
You've become something
of a legend around here.
And you!
Who are you?
♪
Where are my manners?
We rarely have guests here,
I'm a little out of practice.
I'm Raremaro Tefuanokimi,
the student council
president of Sengoku.
Where do I know that name?
I can't place it, huh?
♪
I see our guests
arrived in one piece.
Hey, it's that
Sky Ninja Yamigarasu!
The one who brought
us crashing down.
I merely subdued an
unauthorized intruder.
Name's Kanahebi, resident
advisor of the dorms.
Although I've
introduced myself,
I didn't explain
my position yet.
I'm in charge of the
disciplinary committee
here at Sen‐cad.
Basically, you're looking at
the people who run this school.
Sort of like your
student council.
You can relate
to that, right?
I guess.
Except that here it looks like
the strongest students rule.
Yes, very well put, my dear.
We're so strong
and powerful
that people are calling
us the Four Demons,
or the Four
Demon Generals.
I'm bad at math, but I only
count three of 'em, yo.
I think the last one's
making his big entrance now.
Toku‐chu!
(crying, grunts)
Stop that
this instant!
What's the big
idea, missy?
My Kemura caught this
smelly octopus yesterday
and is planning on having
it for breakfast, you hear?
Takosuke is not an
octopus, he's my buddy!
Yeah, you don't
want to eat that.
He's the fourth member?
You'd better believe it!
My Kemura is wicked strong!
(croaking laugh)
So, tell me, if you guys,
you know, know everything,
then where's Rouga
keeping our friend
he brought
here yesterday?
Huh?
Who's Rouga?
I've never heard
of him, have you?
Don't play dumb!
Takosuke's presence
here is proof
that you know
what's going on!
My friend's name
is Kiri Hyoryu.
We came here to take him back
home with us where he belongs!
Now, please, tell
us where he is.
You sure are persistent.
‐I know that voice!
‐Sounds like Rouga!
♪
He looks so
impressive.
It's him alright.
He may have scored
some upgrades,
but he's still got that
sketchy vibe going on.
Not just that.
You look like
you've seen a ghost.
Nah, just
thinking out loud.
Come on, give
it up, Rouga!
Where is Kiri?
I'm happy to tell you, but
this is Sengoku Academy.
You must follow our traditions
like everyone else.
Bring it on!
We'll enjoy beating
you in a Buddyfight
if it means
getting him back.
Perfect, but be warned.
You're a long way
from Aibo Seifukai.
We do things a little
differently here.
Hmm.
If I may, Rouga,
you're still new here
and might be unaware
that we have regulations
preventing us from
doing whatever we‐‐
I've been here
long enough to know
that winning Buddyfights
is everything.
Hmm!
But I'm a reasonable guy.
I don't need to fight
all of them myself.
Let's have a
team challenge.
Five against five.
I like you, Aragami.
You're a real proactive
thinker, you know that?
I have no objections.
It'll be fun matching
wits with Aibo's best.
Ribbit, ribbit.
That makes
it unanimous.
Do you accept
our terms, Mikado?
If you defeat us, I'll tell
you whatever you wish to know.
Even if it surprises you.
Deal! We'd never
back down from a fight.
It's gonna be
a team match!
Five of our best
fighters are up against
five top fighters
from Sengoku Academy
in the secluded mountains
of beautiful Chohakone!
♪
So, who's going first?
Raremaro, it's not
really your style, is it?
‐How about you Kemura?
‐Ribbit.
He's still in a bad mood
because he didn't get
to eat that big pink
octopus for breakfast.
I'll do it.
Yeah, go on, show us
how it's done, Aragami!
Do your new
school proud.
Which one of us
should go first?
It looks like they're
sending out Rouga.
Whoever fights him is gonna
have a very tough battle.
Hey, I'll do it!
I can take him down.
‐Huh?
Alright, go get
him, Tetsuya!
Okay, A‐dog,
buddy skill on, yo!
You got it.
Buddy skill on!
Ha ha!
Yeah!
(laughing)
That's crazy,
a flying banana?
I decided that he was
finally ready to use it.
Hear that?
Hmm!
Sure? He beat
you last time.
This'll be
different, yo.
I wasn't just practicing
my flows in that studio.
Ain't that right, word!
♪
Here we go!
Up first for Aibo
is Tetsuya Kurodake
and in an interesting
turn of events,
Sengoku's sending out
former Aibo student,
Rouga Aragami.
Come on, move,
dancing demon!
It's time to groove!
Let's luminize it, yo!
The power of Ace
will destroy you.
Dark Luminize!
Ace, defeat!
Buddyfight!
‐It's time to raise the flag.
Magic world!
Danger world!
(grunts)
Tetsuya will go first.
Charge and draw!
What's this?
I can't step it up
with just one monster.
Keep your cool.
This'll work.
I cast!
Let's have some fun
and activate Nice One!
Are you sure
about this, Tets?
I'm hyped.
Now I got the
ultimate hand, yo!
What's an ultimate hand?
I don't know.
Here we go!
I call Fallen Angel of Rage,
Beleth, to the center.
♪
The name of the game,
I cast trans‐flame.
Burn Rouga for
one damage point.
(roaring)
♪
(grunts)
Key of Solomon,
First Volume!
It's such a slice,
I'll use it twice!
♪
Have things changed?
I thought the player going
first could only attack once.
Tetsuya's Magic World deck
has a few advantages, bro.
Watch.
Watch and learn,
I'll win in one turn.
Represent!
‐Why you‐‐
‐Come on, fellas!
Teach this
rocker to dance!
Your time is up!
(grunts)
♪
This guy's a joke.
I cast Bold Retaliation!
What a move!
The same number of damage
points Rouga just received
is now added
to his gauge.
I knew it would be tougher
than that to take him down.
Gauge, smage, who cares?
Final phase!
Unbelievable, it's his
first full turn of the match
and he's already
calling Final Phase!
I cast!
And lift off!
Diabolical Hardcore!
♪
The kid might
actually pull it off.
I cast Bold Retaliation.
One more shot and I can get back
to chilling with my main crew.
Two impact cards in a row!
Maybe Tetsuya is gonna
have a one turn victory.
He's sure come a long way.
Diabolical Hardcore!
He did it!
I cast Phoenix Wall!
Rouga reduces damage with
a feisty Phoenix Wall.
There ends the
one turn victory.
End of move.
Aw, I got punked.
I think I've played
against you before.
Uh, yeah, it's me, Tetsuya.
Of course.
Your buddy's that
strange demon, Asmodai.
(snickering)
You're about
to be schooled.
This is how to win
it all in one turn.
I buddy call to the center,
Armorknight Cerberus Ace!
I equip Demonic Spear,
Swirling Darkness.
He regains one life point
with a buddy gift.
Demonic Equip Combination.
♪
And Mind‐Blowing
Roaring Charge.
He's added Cerberus Ace to
Swirling Darkness' soul.
This is dicey, yo!
Rouga had to pay
a lofty three gauge
to use Cerberus Ace's
ability, Roaring Charge,
but it increases his
critical to eight!
Time for Final Phase!
Isn't it a little early
to be trying for that?
Unless he's got a card that'll
give him even more critical!
I cast.
I'll get you and
your little monster, too.
Drill Bunker!
This brings Swirling Darkness'
critical to an astounding ten!
It's lights out if
we get hit with that.
Relax, I'm a step ahead.
I cast Solomon Shield.
You're a fool.
I cast, your
spells disappear.
Let me introduce
Fanged Dragon Declaration!
But I was having
so much fun!
Swirling Darkness
penetrates Beleth!
(shocked yells)
Aragami's a
wolf out there.
Good thing he's
on our side now.
He's strong,
I'll give him that.
Ribbit, ribbit.
One good fight does not,
a legend, make.
Game over.
Winner: Rouga Aragami.
♪
You're no challenge for me,
Asmodai's buddy.
Go on, bring out
someone with skill.
♪
Now it's personal.
It's time for...
Tasuku and Gao's...
‐Card of the Day!
This week, we're
gonna start explaining
some featured
cards to you guys.
And today's card is none other
than Armorknight Cerberus Ace.
That's Rouga's
intense new buddy
he fought with
on today's episode!
Plus with a Demonic
Equip Combination,
it can add
two critical.
That's not all.
If you use Roaring Charge
and pay three gauge,
you can increase your
critical by another three!
So what do you
think, guys?
You think you can
open up one of these?
You'll never know
until you try!
♪
Next time,
Genma takes on Kemura.
It isn't the first
time they've fought,
but this one's
going way beyond,
and what's this hate card
that tears bonds apart?
Next episode "Challenge
from Legend World!"
Join us for a Buddyfight!