♪
Get ready for a
cool new card game
that connects to
a parallel universe.
Special cards
act as portals,
bringing
monsters to Earth
to become
buddies with humans.
And through
friendship and courage,
help them take on
fight challenges.
It's called
Buddyfight.
♪
This is getting
really crazy.
First Genma's gone,
and now Doai too.
But I don't get it.
Why did you bring
the deck here
instead of
just giving it back
to the Seifukai?
Relax, little brother,
it's all part
of a bigger plan.
You can tell me,
I may be young,
but I can handle it.
If you don't know, then
you can't get in trouble.
Now go on, get some sleep.
♪
Aw, it's just not fair.
Hmm.
(stone grinding)
My brother's lost it.
I really think the Seifukai
ought to have this back.
♪
What do you mean Doai's
been missing for two days?
Why are you just telling
me about this now?
We didn't want to upset you
before your semi‐final match.
Besides, this is
a Seifukai problem.
And we intend to
locate him on our own.
And let me guess,
you can't find him.
(sigh)
Not yet.
But we received this
just before the deputy
leader went missing.
♪
"I thought you should know,
Genma's Koryukien deck
is hidden in the
student council's office."
It's totally talking about
the ancient Seifukai deck
built over generations.
Why would it be in the
student council's office?
Wait a sec, how do we know
this information's even true?
Before he vanished,
we believe Doai went
there to investigate.
But we can't verify it
unless we figure out
who sent the letter.
Uh, Tsukikage's name is
stamped right here, you guys.
‐Tsukikage?
I think it's time we paid
the sender a little visit.
Excuse me, have you seen
my younger brother?
Sorry, no, he isn't here.
Okay, thanks.
This again?
Do we have a
problem here, boys?
We need to speak with you.
Your buddy, Tsukikage.
He wrote this!
It's got his
name on it, Zanya.
Just what exactly
are you up to, man?
Tsukikage found Genma's deck
at the student
council's office.
I don't know
anything else about it.
I promise.
Wait, you mean
Akatsuki took it?
How did you know that?
So in other words,
you guys are
saying you nabbed it
from Shito's office, right?
Tsukikage!
Why didn't you just give
it back to the Seifukai?
Because...
Attention, everyone.
The second semi‐final
match of the ABC Cup
is about to begin!
Players, please report
to the fighting stage.
I better get a move on.
Listen, I can't get
into it now, guys.
Trust me, I have my reasons.
If all goes
according to plan,
it'll work out.
That is unless my
overeager sibling's
done something
to mess things up.
Ugh, why won't you
just grow up,
huh, Akatsuki?
♪
Thank you for joining us.
As you can see, the
first team to arrive
is Naniwa Card Club.
First to show?
Nothing like being
a major keener.
Great, so much
for breezing in
fashionably late
with confidence.
Maybe he won't show
and I'll win by default.
That'd be pretty choice,
wouldn't it?
Before you go,
you had a good reason
for taking the deck, right?
I mean, is it cool?
Of course.
Then give me your word.
It won't cause
anybody trouble, will it?
No, it's legit,
I promise.
Then hurry, you're gonna
be late for your match.
Leave Akatsuki to me.
Don't worry about it.
I'll totally
sniff him out.
Keep calm, bro,
we got this.
Count me in.
What can I do?
The Seifukai will
lead the charge.
Thanks.
Eclipsing the
darkness with flames.
And brightening the hearts
of the mistreated.
The Mighty
Sun Fighter is here.
Team Kisaragi has arrived!
Time to kick off the fight!
♪
You handle
the match analysis,
'kay Kugaru?
Kiri, you pretend to
be Akatsuki in the pit.
Just keep your head down.
And Baku,
search the grounds
for any sign of him.
On it.
Incredibly, both semi‐final
match ups this year
have been battles
between fighters
using the same world.
The first match up was
a Dragon World encounter.
And today, we have an exciting
Katana World showdown.
We'll get to see
how the same world
can offer majorly different
decks of playing styles.
Let's watch the
pre‐tournament interview
with Jin Magatsu!
My deck showcases the
wicked Skull Warriors.
In layman's terms,
it's a deck that
will scare the pants
off of my opponent.
Uh, you know I'm
starting to wonder,
do you think I
need a new image?
You sure you want
to ask me that?
Now, a few words
from Zanya Kisaragi.
What, a girl?
Well, uh, the
ninja's sole purpose
is to defeat his proponents,
I mean opponents.
It's the same for
my Cyber Ninja deck.
If it does the thing,
it will lead me to history.
Uh, I mean victory.
Okay, we'll take
your word for it.
A terrifying spectacle's
about to begin.
Luminize!
Crazy Phantom, Carnival.
(cheering)
Sword of destiny pierce
hearts of darkness and evil.
Luminize, behold the
Kisaragi ninja arts!
(cheering)
Now, yell it like
you just don't care.
Buddy...
Fight!
(cheering)
‐Let's raise the flag.
Katana World.
And the real Katana World.
In a perfect world,
they'd both lose the match.
Shido, where's Genma's deck?
I have no idea.
And I don't
really care, either.
Hmm.
I call Sea‐splitting
Irukamaru to center.
♪
Face me or face
night in the deep.
I chose to pay one gauge
and set Art of
Explosive Hades Fall.
♪
What's Art of Explosive
Hades Fall, you ask?
It's a set spell
that has an effect
of the monster that
Zanya calls to the field
is the same size
that Magatsu sets down.
If it is, then not only will
Zanya's monster be destroyed,
but he'll also receive
two damage points.
What a strategic move!
Talk about puttin'
on the pressure.
If you call a monster
the same size as his guy,
then kaboom.
Pretty sweet, huh?
I can tell you right now,
it's a size one monster.
Huh, what makes
you say that, yo?
Zanya's deck
is usually packed
with strong
size one monsters
that are easy to play.
Word.
Like Electron Ninja, Shiden.
And Nanomachine Ninja,
Tsukikage.
(gasps)
Sword of the thrashing seas.
Ugh!
End of move.
Your move.
Draw.
Charge and draw.
I call Electron Ninja,
Shiden to the right.
♪
Shiden, he's playing
it off the hop, yo.
That's it, Explosive
Hades Fall, activated!
♪
(explosions)
A clean hit!
Jin's masterful set spell
takes Zanya's life
points down to six.
Falling to Hades
so soon now, are you?
Even I thought
you'd last longer.
I'm just warming up.
I buddy call Nanomachine
Ninja, Tsukikage
to the left.
♪
Nin!
With a payment of one gauge,
I call Phantom
Ninja, Kashinkoji
to the center.
♪
Now I can inspect your
hand and see your cards.
Ha ha ha, with
eyes everywhere
and all knowing powers,
Phantom Ninja clairvoyance!
The secrets in your hand
slip through like sand.
With Kashinkoji's
amazing ability,
Zanya's able to
see what cards
Jin Magatsu's holding up.
Come on, seriously, you
really think that's fair?
I mean, seems almost
like cheating to me.
Activate disaster force.
♪
Stellar Deity, Astraeus.
Show me all,
reveal the truth.
♪
Ah.
Tsukikage, attack Irukamaru.
I've been ninja'd, aagh!
Kashinkoji, attack Jin!
Gurenenbu, with dragon
breath comes truth.
♪
That's it, adorable.
Final phase.
Bring it on.
Lethal formation.
Check it, it's Zanya's
specialty, yo.
That's weird,
why did he use it
without making any moves
to set it up?
Maybe he's so
worried about Akatsuki
that it's throwing him
off his game.
Set.
Zanya's playing style
seems a bit off today.
Must be more girls than
usual up in the stands.
Maybe it's you, Mamakari.
Something weird's going on,
that's for sure, hmm.
Even his kid brother
is acting funny.
Wait a second.
♪
That's not him.
What do you mean?
There's someone else
in the buddy pit?
I've just confirmed it
and I'm guessing that
has something to do
with Zanya's lack of focus.
Well, if you're right,
let's shake things up
to make it more interesting.
He won't know what hit him.
Time to turn up the heat.
Cast!
Huh?
A powerful set spell,
Return to the Underworld.
Where are you Akatsuki?
Hey, kid!
Hmm, I've never
been this popular.
Why is everyone
looking for me?
Maybe big brother
ratted me out.
I don't even know what
I should do with this.
There it is!
Using that card
is almost criminal
and it's only allowed with
the Skull Warrior deck.
Return to the Underworld
let's him resurrect
a size one Skull Warrior
on every turn if he wants.
I guess this is
why Jin Magatsu's
called the uncrowned king.
I wonder, has Zanya
finally met his match?
The match has already started!
Sorry, brother.
Huh?
What am I doing there?
♪
Did I use a spell to
transfer my spirit elsewhere?
I didn't even realize
I could pull off
such a highly skilled move.
I'm like the
best ninja ever!
Wait, if that's
the real me,
then the me here
must be just a spirit.
So I guess I don't have
to worry about being found.
There you are.
Ahh!
Activate Return
to the Underworld.
The terrifying
spectacle begins.
Prepare for the
fright of your life.
Buddy call Evil in Heart,
Yamigitsune to the center.
♪
Ha ha ha, do you
fear the undead?
Yamigitsune has
been brought back to us
and with a buddy gift,
Jin recovers one life point.
Yamigitsune, she's trippin'.
He hasn't been defeated yet,
he just got to the show.
(laughing)
You're telling me
you didn't see him
go to the drop
zone earlier, Tets?
When Jin activated his
Hades Fall set spell,
he sent Yamigitsune
to the drop zone.
Oh, sorry, my bad.
Are you even watching?
♪
Yamigitsune, attack
Phantom Ninja, Kashinkoji.
Blue Flame, Fox Fire!
I cast Ninja Arts,
Steel Ball!
That spell increases a
ninja's power during battle
and also makes
counter attacks possible.
I cast, and I'll use two life
for Demon Way, Sakurafubuki.
Sakurafubuki nullified
Zanya's Steel Ball spell.
That means Yamigitsune's
attack won't get through.
Aargh!
You're up, Kimensai,
attack Zanya.
(maniacal laughter)
Aargh.
Sword of devilish delight!
♪
To darkness.
By sending a Skull Warrior
that's caused damage
to his opponent
to the drop zone,
Jin can now draw one card.
♪
And just like that,
my hand's changed entirely.
Looking at my cards
was a big waste of time.
♪
(sniffing)
Well, Drum,
what's the story?
This way.
Good work, buddy.
The center's wide open,
and yet he's opted to attack
Tsuikikage on the left.
Jin's either brilliant
or a complete
and total flail!
Aah!
Tsukikage goes down.
End of move.
Your move.
Draw.
Uh?
I don't believe it,
he drew a second
Electron Ninja, Shiden.
Charge and draw.
♪
I call to the right,
Electron Ninja, Shiden!
I'll pay one gauge to
discard a Ninja Art card
from my hand and draw
two cards from the deck.
And I call Tsukikage
to the center!
Always one step ahead,
Zanya didn't activate
Tsukikage's skill earlier
so he'd be able to call
it to the center now!
Looks like
another solid move.
This time by Zanya.
This is some amazing action!
Who's gonna win
this incredible
Katana World battle?
Go get him, Tsukikage.
Hang in there, big Z!
So why aren't
you rushing over
to the fighting stage now?
To tell you the truth,
I really want to go.
But I don't
think my brother's
too happy with
me right now,
for taking his deck.
Return to the Underworld
raises its head again.
He'll return no matter how
many times he's defeated.
I call Yamigitsune
to the center,
and call Irukamaru
to the left.
First up, the
Irukamaru on the right
attacks Shiden.
Aargh!
Ugh.
Yamigitsune,
attack Tsukikage.
Grr.
♪
Nanomachine
Body Replacement.
It's futile.
Attack again on the
Irukamaru on the left.
(crazy laughter)
End of move.
What's the matter,
can't play without your
brother holding your hand?
Thought so.
Your move.
It's none of your business.
You're finished.
Hah‐‐charge and draw.
♪
I call to the left,
Extermination Ninja,
Slashing Asura!
(evil laughter)
We finally have
an appearance
by a size three monster!
I equip
Ninja Blade, Kurogachi.
With this power play,
Zanya's positioning
himself to end the match
right here on this turn!
Ha, I'll believe it
when I see it.
Hey, Zanya's heart
rate's increasing.
Looks like
something's getting him
all worked up over there.
Changing your strategy
after I bring up
your little bro, hey?
Threw you off, did I?
With your experience,
you should know all too well
about Asura's
powerful abilities.
I activate Ninja Art,
Asura Bacharim
by sacrificing
one life point
and my entire hand!
Ah!
♪
That was a little
worse than I thought.
What a smack down!
Jin's monsters
have been destroyed.
Could the match be over
on this turn?
Where are you, Akatsuki?
‐Come on kid?
‐Where is he?
Where could he be?
Hey, look, there he is,
over there!
(heavy breathing)
What the... he was just here.
Ha!
♪
It's a hit!
Let's see if the
great Slashing Asura
can finish the job.
Watch out!
Quickly, Asura, attack!
♪
Mastering the card zone.
Cast!
Behold the Art
of Body Replacement.
End of move.
The Art of Body Replacement
wipes out an
opponent's attack,
making it ineffective.
Hold on to your popcorn!
You're playing well, kid,
but you've
underestimated me.
Next time you'll think twice.
Draw, charge and draw.
Resurrect Yamigitsune.
Jin uses Return to
the Underworld again.
That should finish
off that Zanya.
Call to the left.
Attack Asura.
♪
You can see it
was a big mistake
to pay one life point
to use Asura's ability.
Final phase.
Thanks for playing.
I cast...
Hey, what's going on?
As predicted, you've
fallen right into my trap.
You triggered my
Secret Sword card
when you declared final phase
and followed it with a cast.
Heard of Moon Fang?
I'll pay three gauge to
activate lethal formation.
Secret Sword, Moon Fang!
Aaghhhh!
♪
Game over.
Winner, Zanya Kisaragi.
With great sacrifices
come great rewards.
Though you seemed
to be down and out,
like you were
off your game,
it was all just
part of your plan.
Not bad.
What a surprise!
Zanya wins
the second semi‐final.
For the first time ever,
the ABC Cup final
will be between
two elementary school teams!
How could this happen?
What a nightmare.
Sofia, where have you been?
In here, Gao!
I found us
some tasty snacks.
That's what you've been
tracking this whole time?
Of course, why?
What are you
doing in here?
We're busy.
Right‐‐we're looking
for Akatsuki Kisaragi.
I saw you with him
a few minutes ago.
♪
Move out of my way.
You must be mistaken.
Akatsuki's in the buddy pit.
Hey, Zanya, I have
a question for you.
Hmm?
That kid who was
helping you in the pit,
it wasn't really
your brother, was it?
♪
‐Of course it's me!
‐Freakshow.
Why would you think
I was anyone else?
Akatsuki?
That was close.
Really, Sofia from the
middle school helped you.
Right, she was
actually pretty nice.
You cleaned up.
Congrats!
Yeah, thanks, guys.
I am in your debt.
But, Gao, don't think I'll
go easy on you in the final
just because you
gave me a hand.
What would be the
fun in that, huh?
Sorry ZZ,
I know I messed up.
It won't happen again.
Don't worry,
it's over with.
You meant no harm.
As for the deck,
just give it back
to the Seifukai.
Okay.
This belongs to you.
Thanks, kid.
Ah.
Uh, what are
you trying to pull?
The box is empty!
(gasps)
Maybe you're not
tough enough for this job.
You should have
kept the deck
and ignored Zanya's
little brother.
♪
What's that?
Who said I didn't
keep the deck?
♪
I think I have
our candidate.
As I see it,
Genma's the best choice
for the Dark Core.
♪
Hello there,
I'm Paruko Nanana,
your guide to
the Buddyfight world.
The ABC Cup's a team event.
When the player's
on the fighting stage,
the rest of the
team backs them up
from behind the scenes
in the state‐of‐the‐art
buddy pit.
From there,
they're able to monitor
the action on the
field as it unfolds
and provide the fighter
with necessary info
and strategic advice.
This keeps
players in the know
on what's what.
It's kind of
like a control room.
Can you open a
buddy rare card?
What do you think?
♪
Sofia activates
Disaster Force
and shows Genma
its electrifying power.
Meanwhile,
everyone's gearing up
for the ABC Cup final match.
Next episode:
ABC Cup Final!
Exploring the
Underground Maze!
Can you dig it?