Get ready for a cool,
new card game that connects
to a parallel universe!
Special cards act as portals,
bringing monsters to Earth
to become buddies with humans,
and, through friendship
and courage, help them
take on fight challenges.
It's called:
Buddyfight!
If I knew this was gonna happen,
I would have made sure Doai
had Genma's deck to use.
(gasps)
Well, it doesn't change
the fact that I'm going
to win this tournament.
Why does Shidou
have Genma's deck?
♪
Crisp yo, I finally got it!
Great Duke Astaroth!
That's legit!
(laughs)
Knew you'd like it.
Besides, the next round's
gonna get tougher.
Yeah, if we keep winning,
we could meet your little friend
here in the finals.
Uh, Tetsuya, who are these guys?
They're my analyst
and deckbuilder,
here to represent
for Team Tetsu and Dai, yo.
I analyze stuff!
And I build stuff!
Bro, I'm seeing double here.
Are they alter egos
of Demon Lord Asmodai?
Mm‐hmm, spot on, yo!
The real one's doin' his thang!
You know the plan;
all you have to do
is win your matches
for us to succeed,
and when the tournament's over,
the one holding
the cup on stage,
adored by everyone,
will be yours truly,
Magoroku Shidou.
But if the plan's going to work,
you'll have to win out there
no matter the cost,
you understand me?
Or should I spell it out?
Huh, well, if I've got
to win at any cost, some of it
should be paid to me,
if you catch my drift.
How dare you?!
I've already given you
more than enough!
This guy, huh?
Doesn't know how to negotiate.
Oh, well, you can't
blame me for trying.
It's been real, Shides.
Don't you see this is important?
Where is your school pride,
you sense of honor?
Commander I, I'm just
outside Aibo Academy.
Perfect, according to our radar,
the unknown monster
is still close by.
Remember, you're undercover.
We don't want anyone
to recognize you.
No problem there.
Huh?
Everyone knows glasses
are a perfect disguise.
I still don't see why
I can't just go in
and investigate as myself.
(giggles)
(beeping)
I've got a signal here
from our mystery monster.
What a total rip‐off.
Why does he have
to make things so difficult?
(grunts)
Why are we waiting?
Azi Dahaka!
Our deepest apologies.
It's proving difficult
to find a new dark presence.
Rouga's not easy to replace.
Enough excuses!
Master desires someone tenacious
and well‐suited for
the Dark Core deck.
♪
Maybe Jin Magatsu
would be a good fit?
He's arrogant
and only cares about himself.
He's perfect for
the powers of darkness.
Make it so.
♪
Let's see what the dice say.
Okay, that settles it.
I've decided I'm
gonna lose my next fight.
And what about your promise
to Shidou about helping him win?
He was foolish enough
to pay me up front
and he won't give me any more.
I always say
you gotta pay to play.
You really do live up to
your reputation, Jin Magatsu.
Tasuku, this is
an undercover operation!
I understand you're taking
bribes to fix a Buddyfight!
I never could figure out
why they called you
the "Uncrowned King",
but I guess here it is, huh?
Well, this is awkward.
You know my name?
I've gotta say I'm impressed
the Great Boy‐Wonder Cop
would know who I am.
We believe someone
secretly entered into
an illegal Buddy contract
with a powerful monster,
just like Rouga Aragami did.
Our GPS tracking
system indicates
that the monster is prowling
somewhere around here.
And you think I have
something to do with it?
You tell me,
but, for the record,
I don't acknowledge
someone like you as
a true Buddyfighter!
(growls)
Purposely losing a card fight
is an insult to your opponent
and the game.
I don't really care
what others think.
I just keep my head down
and do what I want.
If that's true, it's
a pathetic attitude.
You may not be behind this,
but it doesn't matter,
'cause wherever there's trouble,
you can always
be found close by.
Sorry, Tasuku,
but I'm picking up
the monster over there.
Guess not.
I'll be watching you, Magatsu.
Keep those streets safe.
(beeping)
Huh?
It should be right here.
♪
What kind of monster is this?
What's happening?
(roaring)
(grunting)
♪
Jack, no!
(grunting)
♪
(gasping)
Something's wrong;
I've lost Tasuku's signal
from Aibo Academy.
Commander, it's worse than that;
he's vanished from
the planet entirely!
♪
(grunts)
Jack, wake up, Jack!
Tasuku.
(grunts)
Hey, pal.
Where are we?
♪
Huh?
Super Armordragon
Galvanic Featherdragon!
I've never seen the real thing.
We must be in the Dragon World.
It's a battle arena.
Yeah, but why would
you bring us here?
Monsters from different worlds
gather here to compete.
The winner is recognized as
the strongest and is added to
the ranks of Azi Dahaka's
army of darkness.
Azi Dahaka?
We don't want any part of it!
Let us go right now!
Jack is my Buddymonster.
I won't let him get caught
in a battle like that!
I am the gatekeeper
of this arena.
If you wish to leave here,
you must fight me.
(cheering)
♪
End of move.
Wow, is this really
the same kid who used
to be called the weakest
fighter in his grade?
Tetsuya Kurodake
of Team Tetsu and Dai!
Give it up, folks!
Your move.
Draw.
Hey, check it out,
I had no idea Jin
uses Katana World!
For sure, bro.
It's a World that tons
of skilled fighters use
'cause it's the best for making
all sorts of sweet
counterattacks.
Only he would draw Demon Way
Karakurenai right away.
It's an impact card that deals
four damage and can only be cast
when your opponent
has four or less life points
and two or less
cards in their hand.
It's time to knock
those kids out of the running.
I'll add it to my gauge.
♪
Guess I better make it
look like I'm trying.
Buddy Call, Evil in Heart
Yamigitsune to the center!
I call Blood Knife Kimensai
to the right,
Sea‐Splitting
Irukamaru to the left!
♪
Is that a g‐goblin?
No, a Skull Warrior!
A Skull Warrior is born
when someone's soul
is brought back
to Earth as a demon
and that is my monster.
I have risen for battle
and will destroy you.
Oh, yeah, I've been
dying for a fight.
(chuckles)
What's so funny?!
You're freakin' me out, yo!
Heads up!
Huh?
(screaming)
Sword of Devilish Delight!
Ugh, he got me, too, yo!
Kimensai has
the ability to penetrate!
Oh, man, that's not good for us,
you know what I'm sayin'?
Relax, kid, Kimensai
will probably vanish
after this turn.
Vanish?
The thing about Skull Warriors
is that most
of them are destroyed
at the end of a turn.
These kinds of monsters
can only be summoned
to our world for one attack.
No matter how strong they are,
I'm not scared of them!
Whoa, take a look at that!
Huh?
To Darkness.
♪
His turn's not done.
Why'd he vaporize him, yo?
I choose to send
the Skull Warrior
to the Drop Zone
and then draw a new card.
To Darkness
is Yamigitsune's ability.
You'll see that the goblins
aren't destroyed for nothing.
Look alive, kid.
(crashing)
(grunting)
Check out that
continuous attack!
Now, Tetsuya's down
to only four life points!
Hmm, if you had
kept Karakurenai,
you would have been done
on your next move.
Come on, A‐dog,
let's throw it down, yo!
Check it!
Oh, yeah?
I'm gonna play
three games
get this monster
out of its cage.
I call Great Duke Astaroth,
he'll take you to town, Hoss.
You'll wanna surrender
with this homeboy in the center!
♪
Let's feast on some
katana slime for lunch.
(laughs)
That's his new card.
Broski doesn't waste
any time, does he?
Yo, yo!
A link cast is best
for destroying all the rest;
Astaroth pays zero gauge
to unleash my Spell Card rage.
No charging into my hand,
bros, large, draw two.
Ticka‐ticka what!
Yeah!
Increase gauge with
Key of Solomon, First Volume.
Add life with the Key
of Solomon, Second Volume!
A steady assault of spells;
now I get why guys
choose Magic World!
I Buddycall my main man, yo!
Demon Lord Asmodai
to the right!
A Buddygift boosts
his life count to six
and he sends a fierce
lineup to the field!
Boom‐chicka‐wow‐wow, yo, yo!
Asmodai's legit,
you'll see it's true.
One sec, he's there;
hey, what's he up to?
The sneak attack
dangerous backdrop, yo!
Like I said, they're not
destroyed for nothing.
Hey, I defeated that guy.
Incoming!
Cast Demon Way Geppagugiri!
(zapping)
Ugh, I suppose I'm only
able to take out its soul.
♪
If this battle arena
is only for monsters,
then humans have no place here!
Indeed.
We have no use for
such pathetic creatures.
I don't know how
you ended up here, human,
but be gone!
You heard the dragon.
Tasuku, go on.
But I'm not leaving you here!
Why argue?
He's willing to let you go free.
Don't worry, you won't be alone.
Another will appear
just as I did.
Huh?
♪
(zapping)
I am known as Jackknife Dragon,
Findar the 100th!
Young man of destiny,
just what are your desires?
Uh...I wanna help people.
But I'm a kid;
I gotta be an adult!
Can you help?
If it's what you desire,
I shall help you, young one.
I get it, you don't
want me to get hurt.
You're protecting me.
Listen, Tasuku!
It's your destiny!
Your battle must not
end here today.
(grunts)
Time to release
the Future Force!
(grunts)
♪
I will fight you
in place of Jack!
No, Tatsuku, just stand down!
I don't wanna lose him!
He's my only family.
What are you doing?
You're actually putting
your own desires before
the needs of others?
You know this makes you the‐‐
The same as Jin Magatsu?
Yeah, well, maybe so.
But...I don't care!
I choose to protect my family!
(cheering)
End of move.
Wow, after that Link Attack
by Astaroth and Asmodai,
Magatsu is down
to four life points!
Next turn, I'm gonna
finish the score
and represent
with Diabolical Hardcore!
Yeah!
Jin, do you really plan
on losing to this guy?
Let's see, I pay one gauge
and call Yamigitsune to center.
No, wait,
make that to the right.
I call Tempest
Garo‐oh to center.
(zapping)
Talk about a bonehead move.
What's he thinking?
Like Kimensai,
the Garo‐oh card disappears
once its ability
is used, capisce?
If he places that monster at
center and it disappears, then‐‐
Then his center will
be wide open for the start
of Tetsuya's next turn!
He's practically saying to him,
"Hit me with your
best shot, bro, fire away."
What's this?
Is the pressure getting to him?
Has he totally lost it?
What a dunce!
What's Magatsu thinking?
I pay one gauge
and activate Garo‐oh's ability.
(growls)
First, Yamigitsune,
attack Astaroth!
(speaking encantations)
♪
You came back again
with Soul Guard, yo.
I'll end it with Garo‐oh.
(grunts)
As you can see, Garo‐oh's
ability increases his power
and gives him double attack.
No!
Yamigitsune, now, To Darkness.
So, what's the deal
over there, short stuff?
Your Buddy trying
to win or not?
You were eavesdropping.
I'll admit I may have
overheard a thing or two.
♪
With To Darkness,
a Skull Warrior
that's caused damage
to an opponent
can be sent to the Drop Zone
and then one card can be drawn!
♪
What's this?
It looks like the sun.
(gasps)
Hey, man, I'm really
looking forward to seeing you
Buddyfight in
the big tournament!
Gaou.
With the effect of To Darkness,
you can draw one card,
just so you know.
(gasps)
♪
I drew it, I really drew it!
Karakurenai.
Now that I've drawn it,
what do I do?
I can't believe it!
I guess somewhere
deep down I really did want
to play this card.
Karakurenai can only be played
when both centers are open.
You gotta think
this happened for a reason!
Why do you say that?
I saw him up there,
the Sun Fighter!
I have to win this match now,
'cause I seriously wanna
beat him in the final.
That's the spirit
I like to see.
Tetsuya, we lost this one.
Say what?
Don't worry about it.
It'll make you stronger.
(grunting)
You didn't think you'd
be any match for me,
did you, human?
Not yet.
That's enough, you must go!
Do you remember back
when we were both rookies
on the Buddy Police Force, Jack?
We were sent out to recover
the stolen core deck case
and found ourselves surrounded
by that gang
of criminal fighters.
(blasts)
♪
Cast!
(explosion)
But you no longer
have that card.
The moment our powers
fused together as one,
that card was born.
Tasuku, do you
believe that a miracle
can really happen again?
We won't know until we try.
We've been through
too much to give up now.
Let's put our strength together!
We can't quit this
without a fight!
Okay.
Here's to going out
with a major bang.
Strength!
New Strength!
(zapping)
Look, we have a new Impact Card!
(roars)
Galvanic Thunder!
Huh?
I cast!
♪
Let's combine both
our energies to become one!
(roars)
♪
Impact!
DRAGONIC PUNISHER!
♪
Forgive me.
I always believed humans
were inferior to our kind.
But who would have known
there are those who
can bond their powers
to the power of a monster?
♪
I am defeated and my
life belongs to you.
♪
Let's go home.
Yeah.
Final phase!
And I cast!
Huh?
One who calls forth calamity,
this world shall be tainted red!
Demon Way Karakurenai!
(whooshing)
♪
Game over.
Winner: Jin Magatsu.
(cheering)
Awesome, talk about
a finishing move!
♪
What do you mean,
you still don't know
the whereabouts of Genma?
‐A message?
‐From who?
Silence!
"Dear Seifukai,
I thought you should know
that Genma's Core Yukian deck
is hidden in
the Student Council's office."
What the...?
So, pulling that card
made you change your mind
about throwing the fight?
I guess.
♪
I'm sorry for
suspecting you earlier.
It didn't really bug me much.
I'm used to people
accusing me of stuff.
I see you won your match.
Yeah, I guess the sun
was in my eyes.
♪
You must never have
that problem, eh, Mamakari?
(Mamakari groans)
Magatsu's true qualities
reflect the goodness of light
that works firmly
against the dark core!
There's no way.
Light within darkness,
now that would be
the most suitable
for the dark core!
The clock is ticking, Shidou.
That was a close one,
but that monster
is still on the loose.
Tasuku!
I'm so glad you're back!
Are you hurt,
are you all right?
Yeah, I'm fine.
Tasuku, why didn't you call in?
Where did you go,
what happened to you?
Kind of a long story,
but, whatever, we got time.
Hello there!
I'm Paruko,
here to guide you
through the world
of Buddyfight!
So, how about that
Tasuku Ryuuenji, eh, guys?
And that Jackknife Dragon!
They made a new impact card.
I guess that's how they formed
Gargantua Punisher, too.
Wish I had skills like that.
Now I totally understand
why both of them are working
for the Buddy Police.
I tell you one thing,
I wouldn't wanna be
a criminal fighter
facing those two.
Can you open a Buddy Rare Card?
Why do you think?
♪
Don't miss it when Noboru Kodou
takes on Magoroku Shidou.
There was a strange connection
between these two during
last year's ABC Cup.
On the next episode, it's...
Join us for a Buddyfight!