♪
Get ready for a
cool new card game
that connects to a
parallel universe.
Special cards act as portals
bringing monsters to Earth
to become buddies with humans.
And through
friendship and courage,
help them take on
fight challenges.
It's called Buddyfight.
First off, I wanna give
a shout out to my team,
Baku, Kiri, Kuguru,
and my buddy monster, Drum.
So how'd you win?
What's this?
The only reason I
won that last match
was because of Drum's advice.
I'm not just all
good looks, you know.
Drum's ego aside,
we're feeling good
about the next round.
Wait, what'd you say?
So that's Gao Mikado, huh?
Doesn't look like
much if you ask me.
But you've taken an
interest in him all the same.
(laughs)
I'll need a clever
strategy to throw this Gao.
By "throw" you mean
to ruin him, don't you?
You know me well.
♪
I think I have an idea.
Don't you remember?
Huh?
It was during the
last Buddyfight Gao had
in the qualifying round.
Already down to just six points
Gao Mikado's pending defeat
seems more likely
than tomorrow's sunrise.
♪
Gao!
Attack Gao again!
Cast.
Blue Dragon Shield.
♪
What, what, what?
An unexpected counter spell?
A startling upset.
Gao Mikado just barely
manages to survive this turn.
It was crazy.
Gao dodged a bullet
using his Blue Dragon Shield.
Without it he'd
have lost for sure.
So there's a weak point
in his formation, huh?
Yeah, it's a risk
leaving your center open
on a triple offensive maneuver.
Well, there must be some
way we can strengthen it.
We've gotta tweak
the formation somehow.
Otherwise he's gonna get
his butt handed to him
in the ABC Cup.
If only there was a card
that could provide
more protection
when your center's wide open.
Hm.
Wait a sec!
I think I know a card like that.
Thunder Knights, Halberd Dragon?
Size two
with attack and
defense powers of 6,000.
Now that's my kind of dragon.
Looks awesome, Baku.
Why don't you go
ahead and add it.
I thought you'd say that
so I already did.
Here.
Thanks.
Aside from Halberd Dragon,
we've also added some extra
size one dragons to your deck.
According to my calculations
it'll increase your
chances of forming
a triple offensive
maneuver by 130%.
That sounds great!
And we've also added more
Dragoenergies as well.
All together it's gonna
create a perfect synergy
with Halberd Dragon
and its strength.
Synergy means compatibility
with other cards?
That's right.
I don't really get it.
What part don't you understand?
Well, synergy I get.
But it means that to protect me
this monster will
move into the center
from the right or left position
to take a hit
that's meant for me.
Hm.
♪
Drum!
No way, no way, no way, no way!
It completely goes
against my code
to sacrifice a
dragon to save myself.
I take a lot of pride
in fighting alongside
my monsters, man.
So sorry, but I'm not
gonna be able to use
this new deck of yours.
Gao, don't be ridiculous.
Kuguru and I put a lot
of work into this deck.
Well, I can't just go
against everything I stand for.
I gotta go.
Gao, wait.
(yawns)
I'm starving.
Where's Gao?
Where'd he go?
Hm.
He's got my lunch!
♪
The stolen dragon deck.
Aw, man.
Talk about high maintenance.
This kid's stubborn as a mule
once he makes up his
mind about something.
Hm.
You should be more careful, kid.
Yeah, sorry about that.
Huh.
Dinner's ready.
Huh, Drum?
Have you seen Gao?
He said he wasn't hungry.
Guess we'll have to
start without him.
Come to papa!
Ah, yeah!
♪
I really can't
believe those guys.
Argh!
There's no way I can just
change my whole fighting style.
♪
You're lacking focus.
Is there something
you wanna talk about?
Look, I'm totally fine.
♪
Looks like my big bro's
in for a long class, huh?
Uh‐huh.
Gao, bad news!
Hey, Kiri.
Your card deck's been stolen.
Are you serious?
Yeah, it was missing
when I got home yesterday.
Hey, wait.
What about...?
♪
That sketchy looking guy at
the bottom of the escalator.
Oh, yeah.
You mean Jin Magatsu.
He's in grade seven.
He's called the Uncrowned
King of Buddyfighting.
But he's had no major wins.
He's in the Naniwa Card Club,
a group that
gambles on card fights,
and he's known for stealing.
What do you wanna do, Gao?
That's an easy one.
Get the dragon deck back.
Okay, enough talk.
We are in the middle
of training, you know.
Mom‐, I mean Sensei.
Please, can you let me
out of training early today?
Is this something so important
that you absolutely
must leave to do it
right now?
Yeah.
It's something I
really have to do.
You gotta let me go.
♪
I guess I shouldn't
stand in his way.
He is doing the right thing
by helping his friend
stand up to a boy
who conned them.
If it means so much to you,
then class dismissed.
Yes, you're the best, Mom!
Call me "Sensei"!
Just promise me you'll do it
without becoming
the Sun Fighter.
Not a problem.
Come on, Drum.
I'm coming.
So where do we find
this Jin Magatsu guy?
I'm pretty sure he
hangs out here at the mall.
Is that Gao?
Where are those guys
off to in such a hurry?
Let's see if he takes the bait.
♪
(bell rings)
Jin Magatsu.
That would be me.
I'm Gao Mikado, we
go to the same school.
Friend of yours?
Never met him.
What do you think, Drum?
Aside from stale coffee,
I smell Baku's tool
box on that deck.
I knew it!
That's Baku's deck
right there, isn't it?
Hard to say.
Why not find out by
challenging me to a card fight?
Huh?
You're not afraid of fighting a
middle school student, are you?
Because I'm really in
the mood for a decent fight.
Doesn't look it.
Even if I wanted to,
I can't fight
without Baku's deck.
Actually, you could
fight him with this one.
Yeah, but isn't
that the new deck
with Halberd Dragon in it?
What is your deal, bro?
We built this to
make you stronger.
You're the only one
good enough to handle it.
Okay, fine.
I'll use it.
♪
Good, then it's decided.
After you, tough guy.
You sure about this?
Going in without permission?
Relax, it's Sunday.
No one's gonna know about it.
My buddy is Drum Bunker Dragon.
Drum Bunker Dragon?
What's he up to?
We doing this or what?
‐Time to raise the flag.
Dragon World.
♪
Rookies first.
Okay, charge and draw.
I buddy call.
That's what I'm talking about.
Drum, to the right.
I get one life point.
Let me guess, you want
me to attack this guy,
am I right?
You just read my mind, buddy.
Then let's squash this thief
and grab some takeout.
♪
Drill ram bunker!
End of move.
I got out of bed for this?
Your move.
Draw.
♪
I charge and draw.
Who shall I summon first?
I buddy call to the left.
♪
Whoa.
I get a life point back.
I call Thousand Rapier Dragon
to the right position.
And I'll equip
Dragonblade, Dragofearless.
♪
The triple offensive maneuver.
Thousand Rapier,
attack Gao's Drum Bunker Dragon.
Gladly.
Stay still.
Infernal veritas.
I'm back.
You're up, Drum Bunker.
Take down your lookalike.
♪
Uh‐oh.
No!
No, Drum!
Instead of worrying
about your buddy,
worry about your life points.
End of move.
Your move.
Draw.
Charge and draw.
♪
Why is he stopping?
He's probably not sure
if he wants to call
Halberd Dragon or not.
You mean there's a chance
that he might not use it?
Mhmm.
Any day now, tough guy.
I choose to call Thunder
Knights, Halberd Dragon
to the right.
And Double Sword
Dragon to the left.
♪
I'll equip Steel
Fist Dragoknuckle.
♪
That's the real Gao formation.
Halberd, attack Jin Magatsu.
♪
Okay, you're up, Double Sword.
Attack Thousand Rapier.
♪
En garde!
Nice try.
♪
Remember me?
End of move.
(laughing)
That makes it even.
You're good.
Best fight I've had in ages.
His life count's down to four
and he's laughing about it.
What a weirdo.
I call to the right position
Systemic Dagger.
And now I think I'll cast
Dragonic Grimoire.
It's a waste throwing
away my hand like this.
But I can't very well win with
just monsters alone, you know.
I've never heard of
Dragonic Grimoire.
It's a spell.
Basically like a card exchange.
It lets you throw
away your entire hand
and draw three new cards.
Argh!
Do something!
End of move.
Oh man, I can't watch anymore.
How is he gonna win
when he's only got
one life point left?
Gotta say, tough guy.
I think I've won the match.
But there's a small chance
you could still bounce back
if you used an all out
attack on your next turn.
So what's it gonna be?
Sounds like you
want me to do that.
You think I'm baiting you?
I bet you probably got a
counter spell in your hand.
Am I right?
Are you going to attack or not?
I gotta.
If I don't I can't win.
So then hurry it up.
If you don't have a
counter card in your hand
I win.
I'm gonna send over
Double Sword Dragon
to attack you first.
♪
Halberd, attack.
Steel Fist Drago‐‐
Cast Green Dragon Shield!
By using Green Dragon Shield
I recover one life point.
End of move.
Face it.
You've got lots to learn.
Gao Mikado, listen.
Hm?
It's time for you
to use my ability.
I can't.
I'm not gonna use you
to take a hit for me.
Boy, all the rumors I
heard about you are true.
You're too soft to be a
champion of the ABC Cup.
You might as well just
withdraw from the tournament.
Gao Mikado, please.
Am I correct in understanding
that you refuse to
call forth a dragon
to protect you from harm
no matter what happens?
Yeah.
But don't you see?
Acting as shields to
protect our comrades
is the way we dragons
of the Halberd Clan
are trained to fight.
I know, but...
It would be dishonorable for
me not to use my strength.
I was created to protect you.
Unleash my abilities and
you'll achieve victory here.
Huh?
Please can you let me out
of training early today?
Is this something so important
that you absolutely
must leave to do it
right now?
I guess doing the right thing
is what's most important.
I don't want to
offend Halberd Dragon
and the guys did work hard
making this deck for me.
I'll do it to win this battle.
And get Baku's deck back.
I'm so sorry
about that, Halberd.
But now I understand
exactly what I gotta do.
Let's win this thing.
Thank you.
You won't be sorry.
Halberd Dragon,
move to the center.
♪
I would use all of my
power to protect you,
Gao Mikado.
He did it!
Halberd's defense is 6,000.
And Drum Bunker's
attack is only 5,000.
You should have played that
card a little earlier, kid.
I cast Dragoenergy
to Drum Bunker.
Drum Bunker's attack
power is now 8,000.
Oh, no!
I cast Dragoenergy!
(roars)
He didn't!
Dragoenergy gives Halberd
the ability to counter attack.
♪
Systemic Dagger, Dragofearless,
link attack against
Halberd Dragon.
I cast Dragon Breath
on Systemic Dagger.
♪
End of move.
Your move.
Thanks a lot for
protecting me, Halberd.
You rock.
It's been an honor
and a privilege.
And now it's your turn.
Yeah, it's my turn.
Leave it to me.
Draw.
Charge and draw.
Halberd Dragon,
move to the right.
Ready or not, here I come.
Come on, show me
what you've got.
He's as good as done.
Steel Fist
Dragoknuckle!
♪
Game over.
Winner, Gao Mikado.
Dang, yo.
Man, that was a close one.
I don't believe it.
This is Jin Magatsu
we're talking about.
Oh.
It seems the skills
of your classmate
are far greater than
I had first thought.
Sorry, but that's the best I
could do without my own deck.
Baks, my man.
Was that good enough?
Baks?
You mean...
(laughing)
‐It was all an act?
Sorry, bro, but
it had to be done.
Our bad.
Yeah.
I'm sorry.
Baks and I actually go
back a pretty long way.
He did what he thought was best.
You should forgive him, Gao.
You, too, Drum is it?
The name's Son of
Drum Bunker Dragon
Fang Slade Terrestrial XIII!
And don't you forget it.
All right, I got it.
I'll remember.
First time for everything.
I'm the one who should be
apologizing to you guys.
I mean, I didn't
even listen to you.
No worries.
Thanks to this deck
I fought with Halberd Dragon.
And I'm really glad I did.
Because now I get that
sometimes you gotta do
what you gotta do.
Doing things for each other
is what makes us a team.
Yeah, you're right.
So where's the deck?
It's all yours.
Here.
You know, I really
gotta hand it to you.
Sure had me believing
you stole it from us.
I'm theatrically inclined.
Listen, Gao.
You should be happy
that your friends
went through so much trouble
to do something to
help you out, you know?
Friends like that are rare.
I am happy.
So then you agree that
this is your new deck, right?
No, it's not mine.
This deck belongs to
team Balle Du Soleil.
Right.
Blah‐blah‐blah,
teamwork, whatever.
Let's go eat.
All right.
I just had an idea.
Let's take the Soleil
from our team name
and call it Soleil Dragon Deck.
‐Yeah, I like it.
Gao.
I promise I won't go so
easy on you in the ABC Cup.
Huh?
You mean you're gonna compete
in the ABC CUP, too?
Of course I am!
And not just me.
Okay, you can come out now,
I know you're here.
(laughing)
Quite the entrance.
♪
It's not Halloween yet, is it?
It's Lady Suzuha Amanosuzu.
Amana‐who‐soo?
Wait a sec, that
name sounds familiar.
I'm really not surprised
you've heard of it.
I mean, the Amanosuzu Group
is one of the top ten
international super companies.
It's the largest transportation
equipment manufacturer
in the world.
Lady Suzuha
is the company
founder's only daughter.
Gao Mikado.
It has been my pleasure
to observe your card fighting
skills here this afternoon.
But after watching you
fumble your way along
I am most certain that
I can tear you to pieces
in a Buddyfight.
You think so, huh?
I must say that that
was a most elegant
declaration of war, Lady Suzuha.
You agree with me,
of course, don't you?
Student Council President.
Of course, my lady.
Forgive me for being so bold,
but you're looking
particularly radiant today.
Magoroku Shido.
What exactly is he doing here?
Our three teams,
along with team Seifukai,
will be the four teams
representing the middle school
in the tournament.
Seifukai?
They uphold the moral
standards of the Academy.
The group members are mainly
from the school cheering squad.
They're given the
special privilege
of being able to
participate in the ABC Cup
without having to
compete in the qualifiers.
So what you're saying is
they're pretty powerful, huh?
Yes.
Without question.
(laughs)
It's gonna be an
interesting tournament.
I can't wait to shred
those middle school guys
with this Soleil Dragon Deck.
♪
So ABC Cup...
...bring it on.
Hello there, I'm Paruko
here to guide you through
the world of Buddyfight.
I'd like to introduce you
to the pride of Aibo Academy,
our one and only world
famous fighting stage.
It's a massive stadium
that has a super cool
elevated battle ground
that was built exclusively
for Buddyfighting.
The upper level
has enough seating
for well over 1,000
cheering spectators.
I know that sounds like a lot,
but you better try
and get there early
if you wanna make sure
you get a decent spot.
Can you open a buddy rare card?
What do you think?
While the other
humans are celebrating
the night before ABC Cup,
Noboru Kodo learns the
truth about Tasuku Ryuenji.
And it'll surprise you.
The card of heroes.
It's party time, people.