Do you have what it
takes to Buddyfight?
Choose your favorite world,
and use special cards
to summon its powerful
monsters into reality.
Challenge other
fighters and Buddy Call
your toughest ally
to fight by your side.
Get ready to raise the flag!
♪
You know I'll never join you.
Give it up, Coach.
Cut your ties with Disaster.
♪
The decks you build are too
supportive of their fighters.
Huh?
You're confused, people
should not use decks.
Decks should use people.
Decks should use people?
Ah, no way, I won't
agree to that.
Hmm.
I guess the next time
we meet, we'll be enemies.
♪
Hmph, I cast Nightmare Despair.
(screaming)
♪
Axe Dragon Dorcas, you don't
want to attack me, do you?
You're my Buddy.
We're on the same side!
Wake up, your lame excuse
for a Buddy has now become
my very own puppet
of destruction.
(grumbling)
No, Dorcas, don't do it!
(screaming)
Game over, winner,
Magoroku Shido.
(cheering)
I told you my son would
be able to deliver.
(maniacal laughing)
(screaming)
Unleash Slow Pain Fall.
Game over, winner,
Davide Yamazaki.
How'd my life points drop
to zero so fast, huh?
Because I'm just too strong
for you, criminal fighter,
(maniacal laughing)
In the second elimination
match of the very first round,
the ruthless Team Darkness
Masterminds has just
defeated Team Three
Brothers Konmae.
The crowd is an uproar,
but it sure doesn't sound
like a celebration.
We go now inside the
stadium for an update
from Paruko Nanana.
Thanks, Ms. Hanada.
I'm here live at the Aibo
Academy fighting stage.
As you can probably tell by
the murmuring in the crowd,
the collective mood here is
one of outrage and disbelief.
Everyone's cranky about
Team Darkness Masterminds
and their use of cards
from Darkness Dragon World.
Some are calling for
their disqualification.
Why are these fighters
allowed to be using
Darkness Dragon World when
Earth doesn't even have
any intel on it?
Uh...
We demand an explanation
from the Buddy Card Office.
As this was your idea,
I think it will be best
for you to respond.
I'll do it.
Hmmm.
Ladies and gentlemen, I
appreciate your concern.
It's very touching,
but please don't worry.
Earth and Darkness
Dragon World have
recently established
a diplomatic agreement.
We were waiting until today
to tell everyone the big news,
isn't that right,
Examiner Shido?
Yes, indeed!
We wanted to surprise you all.
We have several other
surprises in store
for you during the tournament.
Our goal is to make this first
Gaen Cup a memorable one.
I guarantee by the end
you'll love Buddyfighting
more than ever.
Now, what do you
think about that?
(cheering)
Amazing, only Kyoya Gaen
could keep a secret
of this magnitude under wraps.
With all he's done to help
mankind, it's no wonder
he's just been voted most
incredible person on Earth
for the third year in a row!
Even I'm a little
starstruck in his presence.
Big deal, yo, take away
his name, his bling,
and his crew, and
what do you got?
The way Paruko keeps
going on makes him sound
like some kind of superhero.
Oh, I don't know.
Maybe you just need to be a
girl to understand these things.
I'll never understand them.
It's like they're from
another planet or something.
Nin!
I want to be just like him!
Nin?
He's the coolest guy ever!
‐Ugh!
We have dragons like
him back on my world.
We need to find a
way to expose him.
‐Uh‐huh!
‐Wake‐up call.
You guys didn't already forget?
Come on, the dangerous
investigation?
You said to leave
it all up to you.
But between us Buddy monsters,
it doesn't look like you're
doing any real
investigating at all.
I mean, what have you
found out so far, hmm?
Mmm‐‐word, just in time!
I couldn't find anything.
And you?
(whispering)
Hmm.
Oh, my bad, I forgot about the
other Asmodais running around.
Must be handy.
No doubt!
Yo, you got any clues so far?
Hmm...
So why don't you
become one of us?
‐What?
‐Darkness Dragon World
has some really...
I may have some leads,
but it's too soon to tell.
Better pick it up then, yo!
It's time to announce
the next two teams
in the third bracket
of the first round!
♪
Team Sengoku Academy.
Team Purgatory.
Team Purgatory?
That's strange.
My competitor list doesn't seem
to have those fighters' names.
So I have no idea who's
actually even on this team.
Hmph.
You won't play with
Purgatory Knight?
That's right.
I understand, but just so
I'm clear, you're refusing
to honor a direct
request from me?
No, not exactly.
What, then?
I want to know his identity.
Huh?
(laughing)
Please forgive me.
It's just that I can't believe
that's why you're so upset.
Why don't you just ask
him his identify yourself?
What?
Kyoya, what in the world
are you planning to do?
(chuckling)
♪
‐Grr!
‐What's wrong, Cerberus?
♪
We should get going now.
Our fight's up next.
The order will be me first,
you second, and if needed,
Purgatory Knight
will fight last.
Tell me, Sofia, do
you know who he is?
♪
And you don't have
any reservations
about teaming up with
a complete stranger?
Everything will go according
to Master Kyoya's wishes.
I hope so.
It's not part of my
code to accept mysteries.
I don't care what your name
is, but one way or another,
you're gonna show me your face!
Boulder Piercing Spear, yah!
Stop that at once!
(explosion)
What's happening, huh?
Wait for me.
(panting)
Purgatory Sword activate.
Master Kyoya won't like this.
He gave me
permission to do this.
I have to see if he's got
what it takes to fight
alongside me.
Think of it as a little test.
That's all.
Hey, are you all right?
♪
Uh!
What's with the guy in the suit?
♪
This isn't the time
or the place for this.
Come on, they're
expecting us on the stage.
Get back here!
Rouga!
What do you want?
I've got to know, just what
are you Disaster guys trying
to pull here?
And what, exactly, is Kyoya
up to in this tournament?
Do you think I'm
just gonna roll over
and tell you everything, Mikado?
I have no idea!
But you did help me when
we were back in the mine.
The Grim Reaper went this way.
‐You fool!
‐Ugh!
But last time, you told me
where I could find Kiri.
I thought maybe it was
because you decided
that you were one
of my friends, too.
You're my rival,
and I told you already,
I have no need for friends.
Huh?
Why, what's wrong with you?
I get the feeling that
maybe the word friend means
something different to that
guy than it does to us.
‐Yeah.
‐I think I kinda get it.
We meet again, Gao.
Huh?
Under very different
circumstances.
Hey, look who came all the
way from Sengoku Academy!
You missed me that much, huh?
Yeah, you know it.
Kanahebi.
It's official, my friend.
I'm definitely reviving
the Kanahebi‐style ninjas.
‐Huh.
‐But how?
Well, it's not gonna be
as a criminal organization.
It's a new Kanahebi style, huh.
That was your dream.
Good memory.
‐Hmm.
‐Huh...
Watch out, this
time I won't lose!
Yeah, me neither.
In fact, I intend to show
you my true strength, Gao.
You inspired me to do
a lot more training.
Uh, I don't know,
you were already
a pretty strong
fighter when we met.
As you said, if I was strong
enough, I wouldn't have
given in to the temptation
of the Dark Core Deck Case.
Yeah, well, we
all make mistakes.
The important thing is that
you learned you don't need
the Dark Core.
Indeed.
Is that Immortal
Sword Durandal?
I must say, I was surprised
to learn that Mr. Aragami will
be one of our first opponents.
Me, too, he'll be
majorly tough to beat.
Yeah.
Heh.
♪
Game over, winner,
Sofia Sakharov.
‐How did she...
‐Whoa!
This is completely unbelievable.
The great ninja Kanahebi
was barely able to make
a single move!
Uh, she's strong!
But he's good, way better
than he was before.
How'd she defeat him so easily?
Who would have thunk it?
In a surprising turn of events,
the former vice president
of Aibo Academy's middle school
is one top‐notch Buddyfighter.
She gives a whole new meaning
to the phrase "girl power"!
Hmph.
Next up from Team Purgatory, a
friendly foe and former student
of Sengoku Academy, the
formidable Rouga Aragami!
It's gonna be a tough one
for our team from Sen‐Cad.
They need to win both of their
next two matches to move on.
Representing them is the
oh‐so‐powerful competitor
Shosetsu Kirisame.
Let's see how this plays out.
Hmm?
♪
What's got his attention?
Kyoya, I wish I knew
what you were up to.
You ready?
Hmm?
Let's do this.
I've been waiting a
long time for this.
The power of the Ace
will destroy you.
Dark Luminize, Ace Defeat!
(growling)
A thousand swords defeating
the enemy with a thousand vows.
Luminize, Fortress of Swords!
Okay, everybody, say it with me.
Buddy...
Fight!
‐Time to raise the flag.
Danger World!
(roaring)
I fight for Legend World!
♪
Up first is the
infamously fierce Rouga.
Charge and draw.
I pay one gauge and
equip Explosive Axe,
Ricdeau Demon Slay.
Is it me or do you seem
worried about something?
Don't be ridiculous!
Your mind games
won't work on me!
(yells)
End of move.
That's what you think.
Hah...yah!
♪
I wonder what Kyoya would do
if I went against his wishes?
Ugh, wake up, this is no
time to get distracted!
Hmph.
I call to the right, Knight of
the Roundtable, King Arthur!
And to the left,
Great Magician Merlin!
Let's see how Kirisame deals
with the pressure cooker
his team is in!
I equip Immortal Sword Durandal.
King Arthur, Merlin, do a
link attack on the fighter.
‐Go forth!
‐Yes, sire!
I cast Battle Aura Circle!
(gasps)
(yelling)
(crowd gasping)
Huh?
Oh, man.
How'd he do that?
The power of the
card became real.
Did you see that, Dad?
The spell came right
out of the card!
Th‐‐this is impossible.
How on earth can
this be happening?
Question for you.
(gasps)
Do you really think it's
safe to continue the game
in this manner?
Yes, of course, we have
everything under control.
Oh, really?
If another spell bursts out
of a card, then there could be
real consequences, and
you'll be held responsible!
(wincing)
We haven't had the pleasure.
It's Mr. Neginoyama, isn't it?
You're quite correct,
and your concerns are valid.
However, there is another
surprise that I've prepared
for the fans.
Please, take a closer look
at Mr. Aragami's core gadget.
(grunting)
It's called the
Dark Core Deck Case.
My applied sciences division
of the Gaen Financial Group
developed it.
I was led to believe that any
and all core deck cases are
issued directly from
the Buddy Card Office.
Exceptions can be made,
and this was done
with our official approval.
Just what made you decide
to develop such a thing?
Progress is often misunderstood.
Did you hear that?
You're aware that sometimes
Buddyfight cards connect
to parallel worlds and
cause monsters to appear
here on Earth?
Yes, of course, but‐‐
Then you'll also know
that the mechanism behind
this phenomenon is
shrouded in mystery.
My company was researching this
very thing when, by accident,
we discovered that spell and
item cards can also connect
to parallel worlds.
And in an effort to
materialize these things
at will, we developed
the Dark Core.
As you've just witnessed,
it has unbelievable effects,
but don't take it from me.
Let the people decide.
(crowd cheering)
Oo, so you're saying
that by using those things,
anyone can cast
spells into reality?
We're not sure.
We're currently asking
several fighters to use
Dark Core Deck Cases in
an experiment of sorts.
As you know, casting
spells into reality is
not against the
rules of the game.
However, having just one player
in a match able to wield
such power would obviously
be an unfair advantage.
That's why he's here.
You agree not to use the Dark
Power again in this match?
You got it, boss.
Hmph.
Now then, let's
resume the fight.
All right!!
After a brief but
exhilarating break,
it's time to get
back to the action.
Let's go, Durandal.
All right.
♪
(screaming)
Aaah!
End of move.
Ugh, you've improved
since last time.
He's one smooth operator.
What are you talking about, yo?
I don't think what just
happened was actually planned.
Why do you say that?
Just a hunch, but I think for
some reason Rouga was unable
to control that Dark Power
of his, and that spell card
accidentally activated.
Guess you could say
he's playing with fire.
Ah?
Being the quick thinker
that he is, Kyoya made up
a convincing story on the fly.
Cloud of Doom!
I will rise again.
Argh!
Equipment change, Divine
Protection Prydwen!
(roaring)
That item card allows a
player to pay two gauge
and reduce their
damage by two points.
(grunting)
Hey, Rouga looks
almost as mad as you did
when I ate your last pudding!
Yeah, right, it does seem like
he's kinda worried, though.
Rouga's wiped out all
of Kirisame's monsters!
That Thunder Devastation
spell kicks.
It destroys all monsters with
5,000 defense or less, yo!
Nothing can even
touch that guy's vibe.
His focus is so crazy!
(yelling)
End of move.
Your move.
Kirisame has only two
life points remaining.
This could be his last chance.
I call Galahad to the left,
and Percival to the right.
I discard the Holy
Grail card from my hand,
and Equipment Change.
I return Prydwen
to my hand and...
Who dares to pronounce
himself worthy of my blade?
I have chosen.
I acknowledge thee as my
master, Shosetsu Kirisame.
Now equip the Sword of
the King, Excalibur!
(grunts)
I will use this mighty,
ancient sword to fight you
with all of my strength!
Not bad.
That item has double attack.
Rouga has 10 life left, but
it's too late, don't you think?
Not at all, he can cut
that down in one turn.
♪
After Galahad and Percival's
attacks, Rouga's lost
five life points, and his
opponent's not done yet!
(screaming)
That takes him down to
just two life points!
And for those who don't
know, Excalibur has...
Double Attack!
I cast Battle Aura Circle.
I neutralize the attack.
End of move.
Kyoya Gaen.
Huh?
He is your master, isn't he?
No, you're wrong.
Kyoya is just a friend.
I answer to no one.
Did he say friend?
I think you're lying.
How dare you say that?
Back when I was concerned
only with strength,
and becoming all‐powerful,
you were... well, you seemed
to have an unexplainable power,
far greater than anyone else's.
I was naive to admire you the
way that I did, because now...
Now it's clear that you're
just someone living in fear
of his master!
You've got a lot
of nerve, Shosetsu!
But the reason for
your fear escapes me.
Could it be that you're
afraid of having it all
taken away from you?
That's enough!!
Don't you know that
power isn't something
that someone gives to you?
It's something you
must grasp for yourself.
This Sword of the
King taught me that.
Take it from me, you can free
yourself from his control.
I said that's enough!!
Aah!
Uhh!
(crowd exclaiming)
Not again!
But this time it was
an item card attack.
Huh.
Game over, winner,
Rouga Aragami.
That seals it, it
might seem unfair,
but as our tournament
sponsor pointed out,
this new Dark Power
isn't against the rules.
Rouga's Explosive Axe, Ricdeau
Demon Slay attack has knocked
Team Sengoku Academy
out of the tournament.
Meaning Team Purgatory moves
on to the second round.
What have I done?
♪
‐It's time for‐‐
‐Tasuku and Gao's‐‐
‐Card of the Day!
Today we're talking
about Explosive Axe,
Ricdeau Demon Slay.
It's got 6,000 power
and 3 critical.
When you use it,
you can't call
a monster to your
center position.
But that doesn't matter, man!
Who needs an open
center when you've got
the Gao Formation, am I right?
It's a card that's a perfect fit
for any Danger World player.
Yeah, where power and strength
are totally where it's at.
So what do you think, guys?
You think you can
open up one of these?
You'll never know
until you try!
♪
Next time, Team Seifukai
fights Team Destiny
in the final match
of the first round.
But who's this guy
fighting Genma?
He looks kind of familiar to me.
Next episode:
Join us for a Buddyfight!