Do you have what it
takes to Buddyfight?
Choose your favorite world
and use special cards
to summon its powerful
monsters into reality.
Challenge other fighters and
Buddy Call your toughest ally
to fight by your side.
Get ready to raise the flag.
You want answers?
Then answer to this!
(laughing maniacally)
Hold on, it's that dark power!
Here's Davide!
Future Force on.
(groaning)
(gasping)
I suppose this means I lose.
I don't believe it.
This would mean that Gao...
has the power of Future Force!
♪
It looks like this match
is just about over,
and I can't believe
who's winning.
What a shocker!
Zakoyama's better known
for losing his matches.
I'm gonna clinch it this turn.
But ever since he became buddies
with Bluechase Dragon, Garg,
he's been winning like crazy!
And it looks like today
will be no exception.
Go, Bluechase, it's time
for the finishing blow!
(screeching)
(screaming)
He did it!
Game over.
Winner: Kenta Zakoyama.
(chuckling)
That was a breeze,
I'm invincible.
It's all thanks
to your buddy here.
No way, it's 'cause
of my amazing skills!
You know, if you keep
winning like this,
the Grim Reaper might
make you his next target.
You believe that stuff?
Hey, everyone's talking
about him on the net.
He goes around
challenging Buddyfighters,
then steals their buddies.
That's just one of
those urban legends.
There's lots of dumb rumors
going around right now,
like Darkness Dragon
World being a thing.
(laughing)
If he comes after me,
I'll take his buddy.
(laughter)
Well now's your chance.
I accept your
challenge to a Buddyfight.
(wind howling)
♪
(gasping)
(whimpering)
♪
What, you're real?
Welcome to your worst nightmare.
(crickets chirring)
Huh?
He struck again?
Nin.
Huh?
It's worse than I thought.
He's hit 27 victims already.
Huh?
♪
Hey, don't you go
to Aibo Academy?
What's the Buddy Police
doing about all this?
I've spoken with my father.
All crimes and misdeeds
relating to Buddyfighting
are under the sole jurisdiction
of the Buddy Police.
That includes this
Reaper business.
So how come you guys
haven't arrested him yet?
What are you waiting for,
more buddies to be stolen?
Tell me!
Even though we offered
our full cooperation,
we were rejected.
What's going on at
the Buddycard Office?
Why are you putting
everyone in jeopardy?
Forgive me, but
who is your father?
He's Police
Commissioner Kisaragi.
Oh, well, I don't
know what to tell you.
If nothing changes,
the number of attacks
will only increase.
Why are you just standing
by and letting this happen?
♪
I'm sorry, I wish there
was something I could do.
I thought they called
you the Boy Wonder Cop.
If you're not going to
do anything about him,
then I will!
I'll capture the
Grim Reaper myself!
No, it's too dangerous
for you to get involved!
We'll just see about that!
We'll see who's the
real defender of justice!
♪
The Grim Reaper?
Never heard of him.
What?
You gotta be kidding, right?
You don't know?
That totally weird Buddyfighter
who's challenging everyone.
You didn't hear people
gossiping about him
during first class?
I got way too much on my mind
to listen to that kind of stuff.
You know, like
Buddyfight training.
That's the thing, bro.
If you paid attention,
you'd realize this is
all about Buddyfights.
Hey, that's mine!
Aren't you even the least
bit concerned about it?
I don't know, should I be?
Yeah, bro, thing is,
the Grim Reaper
only comes after Buddyfighters
who have Core Deck Cases.
♪
What makes him so mysterious
is that nobody really
knows anything about him,
except that he
appears at sunset,
ambushes Buddyfighters
in isolated locations,
and challenges them to a fight!
Then, after thoroughly
defeating them,
he takes away their buddy!
Sounds mean, man.
And he steals their Core
Deck Cases at the same time.
The Buddy Police would never
let someone get away with that!
That's what's odd.
The Buddycard Office
hasn't released
any information or
details about it.
See, it's just another rumor.
No, it's not.
Yesterday, Zakoyama got ambushed
and had his buddy and
Core Deck Case taken off him.
That's so wrong!
There's no way we
can let that slide!
Just curious, but do you
even know who Zakoyama is?
Not really, I'm
kinda bad with faces.
Of course you are.
What are you suggesting?
Let's all go to Castle!
The manager's the one
who told me about Zakoyama,
so he might have
info on the Reaper.
What do you think, you guys in?
I couldn't imagine having
my amazing buddy taken away.
It must be awful.
I hope those other poor fighters
get theirs back, and soon.
Why isn't Tasuku out there
doing something about this?
Please, even the
smallest detail could help.
Him again?
Yeah, it's Zanya.
Think, you have to tell
me everything you know
about the Grim Reaper.
I don't really know
that much, dude.
Hi!
Well if it isn't my
favorite little posse.
'Sup?
You guys talkin' Reaper biz?
Yeah, sure are.
Your buddy here
wants to capture him.
As a Buddyfighter,
I can't just ignore
what that jerk has been
doing to my comrades.
We were thinking the same thing!
Let's bring him down together!
‐Not a chance.
‐Why not?
It's too dangerous for you.
And if you haven't noticed,
I always work solo.
Come on, our friend
was attacked!
We want to help, too!
‐Ill‐mannered mongrels!
‐You'll just slow me down!
I know what you're afraid of.
Let's test out my theory, 'kay?
(chuckling)
Ahh, okay, you guys can help!
(glasses shattering)
From what he told me,
Zakoyama was attacked
somewhere around here.
I live really
close to that park.
A lot of people hang out
there during the day,
but hardly any at night.
And with all those bushes,
there are lots of places
someone could hide.
Well, the Reaper's
been attacking
multiple times at
the same location.
I think our best shot would be
investigating that area first.
It just might be
our lucky break.
I agree.
Just remember to
be careful, dudes.
I'd hate to see any of you
get your buddies
taken away from you.
‐Right!
So that leaves Baku and me
to take the west side.
Hang on, bro.
That would mean we're sending
the girls out there all alone.
That's not cool.
No matter what, we need
at least one Buddyfighter
in each group to draw
the Reaper out of hiding.
All right, then Drum
and I will head over
to check out the
west side with Kuguru.
Sounds like fun.
Guess we're together.
Don't worry, we'll protect you.
I won't permit any
shenanigans, mister.
Save it for Reaper.
Let's stick together
and keep our eyes open.
‐Nin.
‐I'll lead us out.
If you see someone that
might be the culprit,
contact the rest of us,
and let's check in
every ten minutes
just to be safe.
I agree, regular
contact is imperative.
Good luck, everyone.
Are we gonna catch
this guy or what?
‐Yes!
‐Yeah!
Maybe I can track this
criminal fighter on my own.
Hmm.
We'll just see about that!
We'll see who's the
real defender of justice!
I can't blame the
guy for being upset,
but it's not like I‐‐huh?
(laughing)
Hey, check out my
double rare card!
Awesome, but I like
mine way better.
(laughing)
I should go.
At least look around.
(sniffing)
♪
‐It's this way.
‐I knew you'd find him!
(screeching)
Am I good or what?
I found the food truck!
This is no time for
snacks, this is serious!
How'd I get stuck
with these two?
Come on, you're slowing us down.
Remind me why
we're running again.
Because exercise
makes your mind sharp,
and we need all the help
we can get with this guy.
Then let's get food.
I'm majorly hungry.
♪
Okay, it's starting to get
pretty close to sunset,
you guys, so careful not
to let your guard down.
You got it, Z.
Good.
♪
Huh?
Is it snowing?
(wind howling)
Who are you?
Ha, your buddy did well
to detect my presence.
Clearly he's too good for you.
Look alive.
I think it's him.
Indeed,
for I am the Grim Reaper.
♪
Hmm.
Uh...
Come on, you guys.
We need to warn everyone.
(yelping)
Freeze!
Sorry for the cold reception.
Can you hear me now?
(laughing)
I hope you backed up your data!
We're about to engage in battle
with unique circumstances.
I certainly don't want any
spectators getting in our way.
What are your terms?
A serious match with each
of our buddies on the line.
And if I refuse the challenge?
You and I both know you'd
never refuse a challenge.
Your father, the
Police Commissioner,
raised you to do what's
right and honorable.
That's why you want a career
where you can help
and protect people.
Either a police officer...
or a Buddy Policeman.
Who is this guy?
How does he know
so much about me?
Besides, if you
manage to beat me,
you might even be
able to capture me,
and there's no way
that you'd give up
such a great chance to prove
yourself to your father,
would you?
No, I wouldn't.
Buddy Skill on.
I'll reveal your true identity.
I'm not having much
luck finding him.
♪
‐Time to raise the flag!
I fight for Katana World, hmm!
I fight for Legend World.
♪
I'm kinda scared.
I hope you don't
mind if I go first.
Be my guest.
Your first mistake.
Now charge and draw.
I equip Rune Staff,
and activate its ability
to increase my gauge.
♪
I set Great Spell Fimbulwinter.
I set two cards in its soul.
If I remember right,
Fimbulwinter's a set
spell that activates
Great Spell Ragnarok,
which destroys all cards
in both players' hands
and on the field.
I wonder if this means
that Grim Reaper's deck
is a combo deck built
around one big finishing blow.
Hmm.
♪
End of move.
Your move.
Wait, how can it be over?
He didn't even attack.
Over here, this way!
It's Drum.
(panting)
Hey, Gao...
Better be the Grim
Reaper this time.
Are you saying you
don't trust the nose?
So he's after the
Grim Reaper, too.
The first thing I'll do
is prevent you from
using your Fimbulwinter!
I call Electron Ninja,
Shiden to the right.
And Leaping Ninja,
Sarutobi to the left area.
Woo‐hoo!
Look out, here I come!
Do a Vertical Straight Line Run.
You got it; get ready!
Now you see it, now you don't.
Buh‐bye, Fimbulwinter.
Ooh, not bad, I guess.
All you did was
sacrifice Sarutobi
to destroy Fimbulwinter.
But my turn isn't over yet.
I call to the
center and the left
Stealth Ninja, Kirikakure Saizo.
I cast Clear Serenity.
Attack.
Follow the ways of the ninja.
‐Right!
♪
Awesome, he did
five damage at once!
I'm not done yet.
Time for Final Phase.
I cast Lethal Formation.
I'm so excited I could scream!
Z's trap is solid.
Set.
♪
End of move.
So what are you gonna do now,
Grim Reaper?
(laughing)
Oh, I'm sure I'll
think of something.
(growling)
Yes, I can already taste it.
You could've at least
ordered some for me
and Kuguru, scale face!
Hope the others are
doing better than us.
Oh, no, I forgot to
check in and call them!
Huh?
What's wrong, don't
leave us hangin'.
There's no answer.
Maybe the Reaper got 'em.
We'd better go see.
♪
Just as expected from Aibo's
best junior school fighter.
You're better than the
other guys I've fought,
but...I think you've used
too many cards from your hand.
What?
With Rune Staff's ability,
I add one card to my gauge.
And I'm going to call
to the center position
Corpse Swallower, Hraesvelgr.
♪
When I call Hraesvelgr,
I can throw away one
Asgard card from my hand
and then draw another card.
♪
I just discarded my buddy.
You know what that means.
Huh?
When I discard him from my hand,
I can choose to pay one
gauge and call him back.
I Buddy Call Ice Blade, Joker.
Brr, it's like
a freezer out here.
There must be some losers
in the atmosphere, brr!
He got one life point back
thanks to his buddy gift.
I call to the left
Stallion of the
Divine King, Sleipnir.
(hysterical whinnying)
By not having many
cards in your hand,
your defense
becomes pretty weak.
In other words, you won't
be able to block my attacks.
Hraesvelgr, take out that
Kirikakure Saizo in the center.
(roaring)
(screaming)
Joker, Sleipnir,
now attack the fighter!
(hysterical whinnying)
(groaning)
♪
End of move.
(groaning)
‐There they are!
‐Are you okay?
Huh?
Why weren't you
answering your phone, Baku?
I‐‐or we were so
worried about you.
We thought maybe the
Grim Reaper had gotten you.
Weird, I must have dropped
my phone while I was running.
Oh, I found it, Kazane.
Nice going, Blade.
I thought you guys
found the Grim Reaper.
I wish, bro.
Have you guys heard
from Zanya or Akatsuki?
Uh...nothing yet, I'm afraid.
(beeping)
They're not answering either.
It might not mean anything.
They could've dropped
their phone, too.
I got a bad feelin'.
I Buddy Call to the center
Nanomachine Ninja, Tsukikage.
Nin!
That's it, throw it
back in his face!
Shiden, Tsukikage,
do a link attack.
Wipe out Hraesvelgr.
Nin.
(screaming)
Now focus your skills
on the fighter!
(shouting)
‐Huh.
‐End of move.
I know that sound.
Someone's over
there Buddyfighting.
I bet it's him!
Rune Staff's ability!
What to do, what to do?
Ah, I cast.
You've fallen
right into my trap.
I pay three gauge and
activate Lethal Formation.
Secret Sword Star Crusher!
Yah!
♪
(groaning)
Come on now, Final Phase.
This match is in the bag.
Ooh, I'm scared,
or at least I would be
if I was anyone else.
But nothing can stop me.
Then take off
that mask of yours.
(laughing)
You'd like that, wouldn't you?
You're the one who
fell into my trap.
You're strong,
I'll give you that,
but in the crucial
moments of the match,
you're weak.
‐You know it.
‐How dare you?
Why else do you think you're
ranked first in your class
but still can't win the ABC Cup?
Because you always choke
when it matters the most.
I set the spell Gleipnir
and I place a powerful
Size 3 monster
from my drop zone into its soul.
Sleipnir, attack Tsukikage.
(hysterical whinnying)
No, you don't!
Nanomachine Body Replacement.
Nin!
Okay, Joker, give
Tsukikage the freeze.
It's what I do best.
Some might even say
it's my speciality.
Nin!
But now you have no monsters
you can attack me with,
meaning that I win!
Think again; you have
much to learn, Zanya.
I cast,
using Breathen Gard.
So chilling,
a Size 3 monster
appears without
paying any gauge!
I've never seen
a combo like this before!
(howling)
Huh, it's Demon Wolf, Fenrir.
That's not even the best part.
When Berserk Gard's
in my drop zone,
I can pay two gauge to
discard one card from my hand
and return Breathen
Gard to my hand.
But we both know there's more
to it than that, don't we?
Don't push me!
I pay one gauge
and call to the left.
It's Joker times two!
I'm twice as bold
but not nearly as cold.
So they say.
You do fairly well
at Buddyfights
because you're smart and
a good student of the game,
but you'll never be
great and you know it.
You should give up now and
save yourself the embarrassment.
First, tell me who you are.
Ooh, I'm ready to feed!
(growling)
Do everybody a favor.
Make this your last match
and quit Buddyfighting.
(growling)
Howling Moon Blast!
(groaning)
♪
(screaming)
Glacier Slice!
Game over.
Winner: Grim Reaper.
But he had him.
Look, it's Zanya!
Who's he fighting?
We were too late!
Zanya!
Stop now!
What are you doing here?
Same thing as you.
Tasuku, am I ever happy
to see the Buddy Police.
♪
He just told me he's going
to quit Buddyfighting.
No way.
I guess you won't
be needing Tsukikage
or a Core Gadget
anymore, will you?
No, Tsukikage!
♪
It was nice doing
business with you.
You can't.
Tasuku, please, do something!
Sorry, I can't.
(groaning)
(shouting)
Freeze, freeze!
Or I'll put you on ice.
You're Ice Blade, Joker!
(groaning)
Gao, you should use your power.
What do you mean, what power?
Forget it, don't you
see what this means?
If that monster's
the Reaper's buddy,
then the Reaper must be Kiri.
(groaning)
(wind howling)
What's happening?
‐It's a blizzard.
‐It was so nice out.
Our work is done here.
Remember, kids, Joker loves you.
I only have ice for you.
I'll be here all week.
Gotta fly!
Don't worry, I'll be back
to take your buddies, too.
(laughing)
Tsukikage, bring him back!
(sighs)
Why did Kiri do this?
I don't know,
but I let it happen.
♪
It's time for...
Tasuku and Gao's...
Card of the Day!
Today we're gonna tell you
all about Ice Blade, Joker.
It's only a Size 0 monster,
but it has 6,000 power
and a critical of two.
Only thing is it
costs three gauge.
Yeah, but get this:
With Joker, you can
choose to pay one gauge
to discard it from your hand.
Then you can call
it with no cost.
So the best way to use it
is with the kind of cards
where you need to
discard from your hand.
So what do you think, guys?
Think you can open
up one of these?
You'll never know until you try!
♪
Next time, Tasuku
drops in on Gao
to talk about some
important buddy business,
and the two friends head off
to find Disaster's secret lair.
Next episode:
Tasuku Takes Charge!
Join us for a Buddyfight.