♪
Do you have what it
takes to Buddyfight?
Choose your favorite world
and use special cards
to summon its powerful
monsters into reality.
Challenge other fighters
and Buddy Call
your toughest ally
to fight by your side.
Get ready to raise the flag!
♪
Demon Sommelier, Zagan!
‐Yo, yo, yo.
‐Fallen Angel of Rage, Beleth.
Yo, yo, yo, lemme
hit 'em this time, yo!
And my favorite homeboy and
buddy, Demon Lord, Asmodai!
In da house!
I have something for you.
This time, I won't miss.
(yelling)
♪
Here's the finish!
You haven't seen
the last of me.
(grunts)
♪
(cheering)
The second game
of the final round
is about to begin.
But first, after all the
excitement in the last game,
we thought everyone could
use a brief intermission.
This would be a perfect time
to visit the concession stand
and fill up on some
delicious snacks
and check out the fabulous
Buddyfight souvenirs.
Although the suspected
criminal Nobari
was in charge of
the Buddy Police
for only a short time,
the damage he's
caused is enormous.
For some perplexing reason,
he destroyed most of our files,
which included vital
intel on known offenders
and details on
ongoing investigations.
Because of this, finding and
arresting criminal fighters
will prove to be incredibly
difficult for our department.
(barrage of questions)
Hold on, everyone
please calm down.
One question at a time.
‐Okay, that's enough.
‐Huh?
Police Commissioner Kisaragi.
Due to recent events,
our forces will now be
working with the Buddy Police.
We plan to coordinate our
resources in a joint effort
to focus our dual energies
on one common goal:
arresting criminal fighters.
Hmph, I'm being
pursued by the police,
and as luck would have it,
I'm about to go and fight
the son of the
police commissioner
in front of the whole world.
Well, I guess now
that the Buddy Police
are no longer corrupt,
you can go running back
home to your little friends.
Even if the Buddy Police
are back to normal,
this isn't the end.
There are still people
out there causing harm.
We need to re‐imagine things
so we can free the
world of injustice.
You're starting to sound
more like Kyoya every day.
As his friend,
I've sworn to support him
no matter what happens.
Tell me, are you
prepared to do the same?
I knew what I was getting into.
And I won't turn back now.
(door slides open)
(footsteps)
Ah, there you are, my friend.
We have something to discuss.
I came to stress the
importance of your fight
in the second game.
You must win at any cost.
You really didn't need
to waste your time
coming down here, Kyoya.
It's me you're talking to,
there's no way that I can lose.
Well, if you do, then
I'm afraid it will mean
the end of our friendship.
(exclaims)
Hm.
That's just a little joke.
As for you,
there are a few things
we need to go over
before your big finale.
If his plan actually succeeds,
thousands of people
will be affected.
But I guess what happens to
them is none of my business.
♪
Scissors!
Yes!
(explosion)
‐I keep losing!
‐(evil cackle)
Drum Dungeon Blade.
(yells)
Now it's time for
the grand finale.
I cast Battle Aura Circle!
I got a surprise for you.
(maniacal laughter)
That guy's gonna win it for us?
Hey, if that pathetic
monster beats you,
you'll have to find a new Buddy.
(chuckling)
I'm just kiddin'.
(sighs, chuckles)
Then again...
♪
Something tells me that
Rouga's having second thoughts.
Buddyfights have
been known to cause
great changes in people.
Even you were not
entirely immune to it,
as demonstrated by your
frustration in your last match.
I never did like the old grouch.
If you ask me, we're
better off without him.
Well, hello, handsome!
(chuckles)
I guess I'll have
to deal with 'im.
♪
No, I have an important
fight ahead of me.
I must clear my head
of all distractions.
What do we have here?
Okay, don't move.
On the count of three,
we'll sneak up behind him
and scare the pants
offa him, real old school!
No, let him prepare
for his fight.
We really need him
to win this one.
And let's hope that I do.
The thing is, with
that Dark Core of his,
Tasuku will be even more
powerful than he used to be.
‐I guess so.
‐You've seen what can happen
when they make those
cards into reality.
You're right, scaring him
wouldn't have been a good idea.
I know you're worried
about the team,
but I think if you
stick to your strengths,
you've got a great
chance of winning!
Relax, man, you're awesome.
Just be yourself and
do what comes naturally.
Uh‐huh.
And remember.
Us Buds gotta stick together.
Now, lets go beat
those Disaster guys.
Hm.
Thanks, Gao,
I really needed that.
You know, you just helped me
to realize something important.
‐You're a good friend.
‐I am?
Now that's settled.
Can we go have our
pre‐fight feast?
There you are, Z.
We have a big problem.
What do you mean,
what's happening now?
Father's here?
Zanya, we need to talk.
It's come to my attention that
your opponent in the final
is a criminal fighter.
I know, I think he goes by Wolf.
I figured you knew.
How come you don't
ever tell me anything?
So are you planning
to arrest him, Father?
That's what I'd like to do.
But because the Buddy Police
lost their evidence against him,
he can walk free.
Not for long,
if I can help it.
I'm conducting my own
inquiry into this Wolf.
I'm here for a
preliminary investigation.
As you know, I was once
a Buddyfighter myself.
By watching him fight,
I hope to learn more
about his true character.
I think I might be able
to help you with that.
♪
‐So what do you want?
‐I want you to make me
a promise.
What would that be?
Promise me that if I win,
you'll go to the police
and own up to all of the many
crimes you've committed as Wolf.
And if I refuse?
Welcome back to the Gaen Cup.
The second game of the final
round is about to begin.
Representing Team Purgatory
is Rouga Aragami.
(snarling)
And from Team Balle du Soleil,
Zanya Kisaragi is
taking to the stage.
FYI, this showdown is
between two heavyweights
from Aibo Academy,
the former top‐ranked
eighth‐grade fighter
and the top‐ranked fighter from
the elementary school division.
We are in for a treat, folks.
Mr. Gaen sure is amazing
at making match‐ups.
The power of the Ace
will destroy you.
Dark Luminize, Ace Defeat!
(growl)
Secret and silent,
but you still hear the sound...
of my mighty sword.
Luminize, Kisaragi
needs Arms Type 2!
Come on, let's make some
noise for our contenders.
Buddyfight!
(cheering)
It's time to raise the flag.
I fight for Danger World.
(growling)
I fight for Katana World.
♪
The first move goes to Rouga.
Charge and draw.
I pay one gauge and equip.
Explosive Axe,
Ricdeau Demon Slay.
And I'll use a Set Spell
final battle skill,
MAJI Demon Slay.
Right on cue,
Rouga's secret weapon.
It's a strategic play
that forces both players
into direct combat.
I figured he'd be going
for the same tactic he used
‐when he beat Jin.
‐Really, why's that?
He uses Katana World.
It's extremely weak in
a direct combat situation.
So Zanya's at
a major disadvantage.
Not really.
Since he found out ahead of
time who he'd be fighting,
I'm sure Zanya made all
the necessary adjustments
when he was prepping for today.
(yelling)
I cast Art of Body Replacement.
♪
End of move.
Zanya used a
specialty of his own
to come out of
this turn unscathed,
with no damage at all.
(grimace)
I cast Clear Serenity.
♪
I call Electron Ninja,
Shiden to the right.
And I use Shiden's ability,
cyberanalyze to draw two cards.
I call Acceleration Ninja,
Hayate to the left.
And I equip by
Heavenly Swords Onimaru.
I didn't see this one coming.
Zanya's equipped an item.
He's leaving his center open
to prepare for a direct
three‐way attack against Rouga.
Was that a happy accident,
or does he actually know
what he's doing out there?
I do power plays better
than the rest of 'em.
We'll see.
You should know that
justice is on my side.
You're going down,
one way or another.
That's the son of the
police commissioner for ya.
The guy thinks
he can beat anybody.
Huh?
Maybe he's figured out
the secret to Rouga's
strategy somehow.
Can someone please
let me in on the secret?
♪
No way, you're kidding me,
Rouga's really who?
You're saying the guy's
a wanted criminal fighter
‐on the run?
‐Shh!
♪
Shiden, Hayate,
attack the fighter!
Destruct‐o slam!
Gale force of steel!
♪
Five Heavenly Swords Onimaru.
Twisted Spirit Purification!
Now I cast Bold Retaliation.
Time for a final phase.
I pay one gauge and set
Super Lethal Formation.
Zanya doesn't waste any time.
There's his favorite move.
This game is officially on.
Set.
If we can just maintain
enough Life Points,
then Rouga will have no
choice but to use his Impact.
And when he does,
our pro will win.
♪
You're better than I
thought, Tsukikage's buddy.
The name's Zanya,
and it's about time
you started using it.
Never!
You think that you can
tell me what to do?
You know nothing about me
or what I've gone through.
♪
Most kids did their best
to move away from the place
where I grew up.
A few of them became
trapped there,
living lives they never chose.
For us, learning people's
names was pointless.
It didn't help to try and
remember who they once were.
Can your precious justice
keep you warm at night?
Or feed you when you're hungry?
Can it make you less lonely?
Well, maybe, uh‐‐
You wouldn't last
ten minutes where I'm from.
To survive, I had to acquire
an overwhelming power
that would destroy all
who stood in my way.
I lived by the code
might makes right.
I call Armor Knight, Eagle,
to the left area!
We've got you now.
And I Buddy Call
Armor Knight, Cerberus Ace
to the right position.
With a Buddy Gift,
he regains one Life Point.
You're up, Ace.
♪
Demonic Equip Combination.
Cerberus Ace has entered
the soul of Explosive Axe,
Ricdeau Demon Slay.
I got a bad feeling about this.
I call to the left.
Devour eagle!
Descend upon us!
Why does this keep
happening to me?
The largest of the
Armorknight monsters,
Armorknight Bahamut!
♪
I always forget
how ginormous it is.
Well played, Rouga.
Nothing quite says
"intimidation"
like calling a
massive Size 3 monster.
It's huge!
Size isn't the problem.
Its power and defense
are both 11,000.
Zanya's in trouble.
Aside from being very strong,
Bahamut also restores four
life points to the fighter.
I move Accelerate Ninja,
Hayate to the center.
It's like that, huh?
Take out Hayate with
Roaring Explosion Surge!
♪
Go with honor.
Thanks, Hayate.
‐I'm not done yet.
‐Huh?
(yells)
I cast Art of Body Replacement.
Zanya not take any damage
this turn either, kem.
He still has 10 Life left,
‐and Rouga has 9.
‐It almost like they starting
from beginning again, kem.
I Buddy Call Nanomachine
Ninja, Tsukikage to the left.
Nin!
Well done.
You keep evading my attacks
and have managed to
maintain your Life Points.
It's clear that you really
want to impress your father.
I'm not dedicating
my victory to my father.
This is all for somebody else.
Well, who is it?
He was a hero with
the most noble of goals.
Someone I've looked up to
for most of my life.
But now he's different.
He's not the guy
I thought he was,
like those kids he grew up with.
He chose to walk
down the wrong path.
Huh?
Shiden, attack the fighter!
Destruct‐o slash!
Tsukikage, get him!
Nin!
♪
Fight, Heavenly Swords, Onimaru!
Twisted Spirit Purification!
End of move.
I must say that when
this game started,
I thought Danger World
had the advantage.
But all of a
sudden, here we are
with Zanya up 11 Life to three.
(chuckling)
It looks like that
loathsome Aragami's luck
is finally about to run out.
If Rouga has any hope
of wiping out all their
Life Points at once...
He'll have to use
an impact card.
And he'll fall right
into Big Z's trap,
exactly the way
you guys planned it.
I get it now.
But I'm a little unclear
on why you want to dedicate
your victory to him.
I was raised to pursue
the ideals of justice,
and I admired him because
he said he was the same.
But then he changed,
and now, I want him to
realize the mistake he's made.
Does that answer your question?
Hm.
Gao's the one who
gave me the idea.
Mikado?
He showed me that in times
of struggle and confusion,
our friends need help.
You know, to get them
on the right path,
to stand by them,
even when they've
made bad choices.
Stand by them.
♪
And I call to the left.
Phalanx Dragon.
Hey.
You didn't pay any gauge
when you called that monster.
♪
That's it.
I'm not gonna
keep quiet anymore.
I cast Dimensional
Demon Slay Slash!
Dimensional Demon Slay Slash
destroys one card from
the opponent's gauge
while increasing the
user's gauge by one.
Attacks!
Now you can't use your
Super Lethal Formation,
and my gauge shoots up to four.
It looks like your strategy
of keeping your gauge
at a bare minimum
has worked against you.
I didn't expect this.
What can I do?
Is this the end?
Attack the fighter with
Roaring Explosion Surge!
I stopped questioning
what's good or bad
a long time ago.
♪
But now I know
what I have to do.
(yelling)
♪
Final phase.
It's time I started
acting like a real friend
instead of a coward.
I cast Ultimate Battle Skill.
MEGA Demon Slay!
(yelling)
♪
Game over.
Winner: Rouga Aragami.
(cheering)
Can you say "surprise"?
Rouga was down
by eight Life Points,
but he's turned the tables
in dramatic fashion.
This isn't happening, no one
can come back like that.
What a nightmare.
Wait, that's it‐‐of course,
I must be dreaming.
Okay, don't worry,
this is a bad dream.
A dream, you hear,
this just can't be real!
With this victory,
Team Purgatory draws even
with Team Balle du Soleil,
which means that next up
is a one match to win
'em all ultimate showdown!
You couldn't script it
any better than this.
Sorry, guys.
I was so close, I just
didn't push hard enough.
It's up to you now.
Come on, you fought
a great game.
Hey, Mikado.
You should be the one
to save Purgatory Knight.
That guy's made up his mind.
I don't agree.
He needs a friend
to show him the way.
♪
What's shakin', Rouga?
Out of my way,
Tetsuya Kurodake.
Uh...
♪
What's up with him, yo?
Why's he gotta be such a hater?
Hm?
You know, I think he
just said your name.
(gasps)
♪
You mean to tell me
that young man
‐isn't Wolf anymore.
‐That's right.
Hm.
I can understand your motives.
But he must make up for
the crimes he's committed,
don't you think?
Sometimes, justice comes
in different forms, Father.
♪
You learn fast,
you know‐‐just like me.
♪
(solo clapping)
You never cease to amaze me.
And now that you've
helped me as promised,
I'm sure we'll
remain good friends
till the end of our lives.
There's something I need to say.
Go ahead.
Kyoya, what you're
doing is wrong.
You have to put a stop
to that plan of yours.
(gasps)
When we were younger,
I noticed a mistake that
you made during a Buddyfight.
I wasn't able to say
anything about it to you then,
but I'm calling you out now.
I suppose you're
referring to that time
I had Dragonic
Charge in my hand.
You knew?
♪
I've always wondered why you
didn't point out my mistake.
Kyoya, don't tell me that you...
♪
Yes.
I did that on purpose.
I did it to test you.
Why would you do that?
You're no longer the
friend I once knew.
‐How very unfortunate.
‐Wait, let me explain.
‐I thought that if‐‐oof!
‐Wait.
There's no need
to erase his memories.
Master Kyoya is right,
there's nothing he can do.
All of our preparations
have been completed.
Even if our plan gets
leaked at this point,
it won't make any difference.
Too bad.
♪
Your memories will be
my parting gift to you.
Wh‐‐what are you saying?
When this tournament is over,
I don't ever want
to see you again.
(gasps)
Don't ever call
or try to visit.
If I so much as see
your pathetic face
within 20 feet of me,
I'll take more
than your memories.
Agh, wait!
You said you were my friend,
was that just a lie?
I don't understand,
I did everything you asked.
How can you do this to me?
After all this time,
am I worth nothing to you?
Nice knowing you... my friend.
♪
‐It's time for...
‐Tasuku and Gao's...
Card of the Day!
Today we're gonna
tell you all about
the Danger World Impact card
Ultimate Battle Skill,
MEGA Demon Slay.
If you have four Demon Slay
cards in your drop zone
and there are no monsters in
either player's center position,
then you can pay four
gauge to activate it.
It's a super‐powerful card
that can inflict four damage
to your opponent.
I wish I could build a deck
full of Demon Slay cards.
So whaddya think, guys?
Think you could open
up one of these?
You'll never know
until you try!
♪
Next time, Tasuku
and Gao face off,
but now that Tasuku's
with Disaster,
the friends are
on opposite sides,
with more than a
championship title on the line.
Next episode:
Join us for a Buddyfight!