I did a mean thing to Iroha huh?
If you were going to feel this
guilty, you shouldn't have rejected her.
I had to. Why would you even say that when you know why?
That's a dick move on your part.
Yeah, well...
I'm flattered she feels that way about me.
But she's wrong.
I don't think... I'm right for her.
You're amazing.
You change the people around you so easily.
What? That's out of the blue.
It's really not. I told you...
I'm not as nice of a guy as you might think I am.
I've complimented you for my own sake.
We will be arriving Kaihin Makuhari.
Oh, great... our stop is up here next.
'key.
Isshiki... My stop is next, too. Where do you get off?
Um.. My bags are really heavy...
Yeah. That's seems like a good idea.
You know... that really sucked.
Yeah. But honestly you knew it was
going to be a bad idea in the first place.
I couldn't help it. Everything was so
exciting, and I just got caught up in it all.
It surprised me.
I mean honestly, I didn't really think
you were the type to get so emotionally
caught up in that sort of environment.
I surprised myself, too. You know I
really thought I'd be a lot cooler about it.
Yeah. You really seem to have nothing but love
on the brain, but I know you can be pretty clever.
This isn't about me... I'm talking about you.
What?
Anyone's heart would start to beat
faster after that kind of display.
Display?
I realized... I wanted something genuine as well.
So, you heard that?
Your voice just kinda spilled out of the room.
Forget about it.
I won't ever forget it.
I'm unable to forget it...
and that's why I thought today
was the day I should tell him.
Well.. Listen... Don't worry about it.
You didn't actually do anything wrong.
Are you taking advantage of my
sad heart and trying to woo me?
Sorry but it's still impossible.
That's not it...
I mean all is not really lost just yet... actually,
this is a rather effective method of attack for Hayama.
Everyone will sympathize with me...
and then hold back to spare my hurt feelings, right?
Y-Yeah.
There's more to my logic.
You worry about the person that you rejected, right?
Like... you'd feel sorry for them.
This defeat has just laid the groundwork...
now I'll try to progress to the next stage.
So then... I... have to keep doing my best.
Listen... you're great.
It's your fault though. I'm like this because of you.
Well... it's true I made you
president, but other than that...
Please... take responsibility.
So um... why did you want to gather us all here together?
To confirm our objective and
solidify our plan before we go.
Okay...
The current plan is completely impossible.
We can only finish part of everything, at best.
It's going to be a pretty pitiful
event compared to how we advertised it.
What do you think we should do in order to prevent that?
Uh... I don't really know.
There's a problem with the meetings.
They integrate all our ideas... but
no one is really making any decisions.
So let's completely get rid of these
indecisions, and have a proper meeting.
We'll have objections, rejections,
but also clear answers to each idea.
Can we have that meeting?
Well then... what do you think about that?
I think... it's better not to disturb what we have.
Trying to raise a counter-proposal like
that now is going to be tough to pull off.
You're right, that's true...
Let's do it anyways.
Personally, speaking... I don't wanna go
out there and put on a pitiful event, okay?
Maybe so...
in my opinion, I was actually thinking a
play would be a much better idea for this.
Imagine if we could have both music and a play.
That would really be a great
deal for all the guests that attend.
I'm not sure about separating.
The synergistic effect will fade,
and doesn't that double the risk?
That may be. But we need to look at the event budget-wise.
We really should think about this as a group,
since this is what the meeting is for.
I agree with that.
Agreed! Agreed!
Tell 'em!
Um, may I ask something?
Why are you against having two
different parts to the event?
Well, I'm not really against it...
If we can join our visions, I think
we can have a stronger sense of unity.
The framework of a joint event is a must,
even if we're just using it to build our image.
Is a joint event even necessary?
Yes. Don't you see that jointly,
synergy will arise out of a large event...
There's no synergy here, and if things stay
like this, we won't make it much of an event.
So tell me. Why are you trying to stick with this method?
Because we took a consensus.
And then we even shared the grand design of it all.
We agree!
Tell em!
You're wrong.
You're all so conceited, thinking we can all do it.
That's why even though you're
wrong, you won't acknowledge it.
You're just really looking to
gloss over your own failures.
Resorting to scheming with all your useless empty words.
Just to gain peace of mind through mutual assent.
It's very easy to do that when
you can blame others, isn't it?
Actually, I feel like this is
simply a lack of communication.
You know what... we should take another cool
down period and then regroup to discuss this.
Agreed.
If all you're going to do is play
make-believe, could you please go do it elsewhere?
From the beginning you've only been
saying words that have no real substance.
Is using words you've learned in a class that
mimics a make-believe job really that much fun?
You speak in terms that are
mistaken for actual communication here.
Which means nothing actually gets done...
There's no way to make progress like this.
You won't produce anything.
You won't get anything. You won't help anything.
It's all so fake.
Yukinon...
Seriously though, would you guys mind
not wasting anymore of our time here?
Instead of working together, don't you think it would
be much better to have our guests enjoy double the fun?
They'll experience the uniqueness of each school. Right?
Uh, y-yes. I-I think that sounds good.
So what do you think? Huh?
Uh... Mhm. You can tell em that, too. Right? Right?
I don't understand why you two had to go and
say all that now! Look how awkward it is in here!
I really don't think I said anything wrong or unfair.
I agree it was a fair argument...
but you really should learn to read the room better...
Or something like that.
If you actually expect this boy here to
read the room, you're wasting your time.
He can only read the lines of text that are in his books.
Guess that's too bad huh?
However, as the resident bookworm,
even I can read between the lines. So there.
Besides, aren't you the one she's angry at?
No way. She just agreed that it was a fair argument.
Therefore, your assumption is unjustified.
Yup, there it is, that's exactly
why she's pissed at you now.
Listen to what she's saying.
Um, hello...
Are YOU listening to me Hikigaya?
I'm talking to the both of you, you know.
Here you go.
Oh, thanks...
Cheers!
Okay...
You've changed a bit, haven't you?
You were just so boring back when we were in school.
Yeah? I was?
Well, I, I mean yea I guess you were...
I suppose its in the eye of the beholder.
Listen., I definitely don't
wanna go out with you or anything.
Yeah, well I'm not asking you out or anything.
True...
But maybe we've got something going as friends.
You're funny.
So do you think you would come to the next reunion?
Nope, absolutely not.
I know, right? Funny.
No, not funny at all.
Could you put it over there?
Hachiman, it's fine.
I've got it. I don't need your help.
Yeah, you say that, but you are...
Go.
Just so you know...
I can do this way more alone than you can.
Seriously though, you sound dumb.
Hey, so you...
That's not my name.
H-huh?
Rumi.
So, hey, Rumi...
Would you like to be in our play?
Yuigahama. Did you finish packing the cookie bags?
Mhm! I just finished them!
Do you want me to help with the cakes, too?
No, it's fine.
Actually don't you dare touch these cakes, okay?
For any reason.
Could you say that in a nicer tone!
Ohhhhh, maaaan! This is absolutely terrible.
The script is good, so you don't
need to worry that much, all right?
That's because our secretary buckled
down and did her best work on this.
And you... you really made it...
Oh, that's right, I'm going
to go see how everyone is doing.
Oh, can you go confirm a few things?
Mainly the final timings for
the show with our vice president?
And also, I'm counting on you for the cakes!
Roger that... President.
Welcome back.
Great work today, Yuigahama.
Ahh Thanks!
What in the world is this?
Well it's a Christmas present!
Don't you know using a paper cup is considered wasteful?
Yeah, Yukinon chose the design. I chose the shape.
Yeah, huh. Not fair, I didn't
get anything for either one of you.
Hey, don't worry about it.
It's just an upgrade from your paper cup.
Well thanks you guys.
You're very welcome!
Oh and... for the request as well...
I really thank you. You saved me.
Because of you it ended well.
The request isn't over yet, right?
Don't you remember? I accepted your request?
Yeah... but the request has been fulfilled and
all. So what is this some kind of weird riddle?
Maybe. If you like riddles.
Oh, I totally get it now!
But it's okay if Hikki doesn't get it... right?
Well, regardless of your confusion,
It's still Christmas, so I
think we should have a party, okay?
No, I don't think so.
Do you have any plans, Yukinon?
If we're going to have a party,
I can keep my schedule open.
Really? Alright then!
Aren't you going to ask me about my plans?
Or is this a case of indirectly
insinuating I'm not invited?
Well... we know there's no way you could have plans.
Oh! I want to eat one of your cakes, Yukinon!
But the cake you ate earlier was one that I made...
In all honesty, if wishes could be
granted for all who desire them...
If I could get what I wanted...
I wouldn't wish for anything. Or want for anything.
The things I can easily get are likely
never genuine. Nor what I really wanted.
And I'll surely lose it one day...
So I think... I will keep searching for it.
Hey, question for you.. Yukinon's birthday is coming up,
when can you and I go and get her a present?
Oh, right...
Are you free tomorrow maybe?
Uh... yeah, I am.
Okay, great. Tomorrow it is then.
Kay.
Oh, it's Yumiko.
Y-Yahallo, Yumiko! Oh, wait a second!
So um... What is everyone gonna do after this?
I think I'm gonna head home soon.
I'm not that good with crowded places.
Aww.. What about...
We'll see each other at school really soon, won't we?
Okay, shall we go?
Oh, gosh darnit! I actually forgot
to buy a good-luck charm back there!
And I also forgot to write a wish, so
I'm just gonna dash back and do that, too!
Oh, if you're going to get a charm, maybe I should-
What the heck are you even saying, bro?
Don't be Brotrash! Idiot! Halfwit! Hachiman!
Hachiman isn't even an insult!
Okay, goodbye Yukino! I'm heading off for now!
What's funny?
Idiot! Halfwit! Hachiman!
It seems like Yukinoshita's insult
dictionary has had a long-awaited update...
I was just wondering if it's okay if we go this way?
Uh... Yes.
So, um... I was thinking since it's
New Year's, you'd be off with your family.
Oh... I'm not going anywhere this year.
I don't really have much going on to be honest.
Besides, in the end it doesn't make a
big difference whether I'm there or not.
Well then, isn't that okay?
It's nice when it doesn't matter if you show up...
because you're not bothering anyone.
There are people in the world
who ruin things just by existing.
Next stop is Keisei Makuhari Station.
So was that a self-introduction?
Yes it is. And that's why I have come to
avoid dealing with people as much as possible.
So.. This is where I get off.
Hikigaya.
I wish you a Happy New Year.
Hey don't I look really intelligent now?
Y'know, the idea that glasses equals
intelligence is already pretty unintelligent...
Shut up, stupid! Hmph!
Oh hey, it's Hikigaya!
Look it's Haruno and Hayato?
Hey there...
Oh, that's right.
It's Yukino's birthday soon,
so that's why it's just you two.
I notice you two always seem to
get along quite well, don't you?
Uh-huh.
My sister was with us earlier, but disappeared.
Who knows were she is now?
However, you two hanging out together is pretty rare.
Ah... we're going to a New Year's dinner party.
Well, actually, our parents have
been close for a very long time.
Which means we're together for holidays like this.
Our parents are off making the rounds somewhere right now.
So we're here just waiting around.
Ah, yea I can see that.
Oh, I know.
Hello?
Ah, hello Yukino.
It's your big sister! Can you come over here now?
I'm hanging up.
Are you? You sure you want to do that?
What?
Hold on, just a minute.
Here you go.
Uh! No wait...
Uh... hello there.
Huh? I can't believe it. Why are you over there?
Uh, well actually... uh, that's
because we're here to, um...
I'll be there soon.
Ah, Yukinon! Over here!
Yuigahama. Wow you're here, too?
Uh I am! Well actually I was
already here out shopping with Hikki.
And we kinda got caught...
Oh. So I see...
Took you long enough, Yukino!
Calling me out of the blue and
telling me to come here is shameless...
Oh now, now... it actually seems like
you got here in quite a hurry Yukino...
So uh what do you want to have to drink, huh?
I'll have black tea please.
It's been a while since we've all had tea, huh?
It sure has.
Haruno.
Oh... have you finished?
Yes we have.
I'm so sorry to have kept you waiting, Hayato.
It's okay, everyone here kept me pretty entertained.
Well.. I'm glad to see you're
here, as well.. Yukino, dear.
Hi, Mother...
Are these your friends?
They're Yukino's friends.
Oh my goodness, I'm so sorry.
You know I've never really met any of
Yukino's schoolmates outside of Hayato here.
I sincerely hope you guys can
remain close friends with her.
'Kay!
So, you guys ready to go?
Okay.
Yukino?
I don't want to...
This is also a birthday celebration for you, you know.
Yukino, don't do this.
These must be my real true colors.
That's really why I couldn't let go.
I locked it deep within myself.
And I averted my eyes from the truth.
I just wanted to be criticized and shown the light.
I wanted someone to see me, see
through the pretentious person I was.
There were eyes looking in from the outside...
and so I held high hopes.
I thought that maybe finally
they might be able to find me.
I really thought they might be able to look inside me.
Reality.
How can you be so sure that it's
not a figment of your imagination?
Is anything really genuine anymore?