Why did I go and embarrass myself like that?
I wanna die! I'm gonna die from embarrassment!!
I don't wanna go to school tomorrow!
I'm so dumb! So frickin' dumb!
Idiot! Idiot!
Guess I'll die.
What's wrong with you big bro?
Leave me alone.
Your big bro is kinda having
an identity crisis right now...
Hey you on the floor there...
Identity crisis? What?
So it turns out that people who go on and on
about their "individuality" actually don't have one...
Plus, how can you call it an "identity"
when you can change it super easily?
Komachi, what's with your choice of words?
It's so rude. And the look on your face is weird.
I was pretending to be you!
I don't sound like that.
I seriously don't know what's happened to you...
But there's no way for you to
fix your twisted personality,
it's too late. You're such trash brother, so trashy!
Then again... I guess that I
really like you just the way you are.
Ah! I got a whole mess of points for that little comment!
Thanks for that little sis.
You know, I like the way I am, too.
I got a whole mess of points for THAT one!
What the heck bro?
Hi Hikigaya.
Uh, hey.
Uh.. So that...
So that... that meeting for today...
Could you please share with me the
place and time we need to meet up?
Oh yeah... Of course.
Would it be ok if I tell you when Yuigahama gets here?
That's fine. Then you don't have repeat it.
Yahallo!!
Hey.
Hi Yuigahama.
Too close.
Hey.. Yuigahama...
do you mind moving away a little bit?
Yeah.. Sorry about that.
I... didn't mean anything...
Yahallo!
We're here to help, Iroha!
Seems like your situation isn't going well.
It isn't going well!
Problem here?
No... not at all.
Uh, it's fine..
There's no problem here.
'Kay, let's just brace ourselves for the inevitable.
Hey!
Look.. We have some new faces joining us today.
Nice to meet you! I'm Kaihin
High's Student council president...
That was so terrible...
Listening to them irritated me...
Totally.
Ok then, what should we do?
Don't know.
Hmmm... Well first..
I guess we should actually
figure out what we can do.. Right?
It looks like you've all finished your work.
I don't think that we had any Japanese assignments.
Then... What'd you come to talk to me about?
So, that means we start with a budget, right?
You guys have no idea whatsoever
what Christmas is, do you?
What?
I'll show you what it's all about.
Ta-da!
Look what I have!
Huh?
Why do you have those on hand? And four of them...
Cause I won these at a wedding reception.
Twice actually...
I was told "You can go by yourself!"
Two times actually...
What is she trying to tell us?
Don't you know after going 4 times by yourself,
it becomes so much fun you'll even pay to go a fifth time?
And if things don't go well but
you go a sixth time, I'll go with you!
Seriously, someone hurry up and marry her already!
You guys take these tickets, go do a bit more studying.
And then use them as your breather...
Are you sure?
Oh my gosh, thank you so much!
Why go now, when it's so incredibly crowded?
I know... I don't really want...
Huuuh? No, it's fine we're gonna go!
Oh, and Pan the Panda!!
They've got Pan's Bamboo fight there!
We can go at any time.
I don't see why we have to go when it will be busy.
Come on, please! They've got all
the Christmas decorations up now!
No.
"Bamboo Fight" uses the same theme all year-round.
Actually.. Their theme attraction has
always been held in the highest regard.
Oh...
You're well-informed.
It's just that...
things that big are common knowledge.
Yukinon, we should go!
Absolutely not.
Come on... I want you and I to go together.
You know.. Since things have been strained recently...
and these are a gift...
Merchandise.
Wha?
The Panda...
Won't they have Christmas. Pan's merchandise right now?
I really wanted to get something like that
for my little sister... as her Christmas gift.
That's great! Let's all choose something together!
Well, if that's the case..
I guess we have to go.
So then... Are all four of us gonna go?
Actually, I have a season pass for
myself... we won't need one of the tickets.
Oh! Then we should get one more person to come, right?
Who are you thinkin' of?
It's. A. Su. Prise!
Hey.
Huh? Hikio is here too?
Hikio! That's super funny!
But he's Hikitani.
Guess what, you're both wrong...
Why are those guys here too?
U-Um... Well...
Because.. We couldn't just ask
Iroha's friends to come along with us!
I mean, I'm in a pretty tough spot too, you know!
'Kay...
Hikki.
Thanks for waiting.
Is her soul being sucked out or something?
'Kay got it.. Here you go Yui.
Ah great! Thanks so much!
Yuigahama...
You know you can't just do that.
Yea but if I ask first, you two
wouldn't have let me take a picture.
That's actually worse.
You can't just take a picture without permission.
Sorry guys... I'll ask you next time.
There's no next time.
I said sorry! Yukinon stop, wait!
Since this place isn't really Christmassy,
it probably won't be a very good resource for us.
Whadda I do?
What the heck do I do?
Hayato!
Hey!
We're riding this together.
Why you little...
Don't you dare.
Hey Tobe...
you're being a third wheel.
But! I'll freak out!
And?
Poor thing.. He's having a hard time.
Yeah well. You should help him out.
Or, even better you can go help
him out! Tobe Hachi sounds hot!
Please, just stop.
Sure.
Let's ride together... 'Kay?
Thanks, Hayato!
About before... I'm sorry.
So tell me, did I really cause things
to get awkward between all you guys?
No, you didn't.
How about you?
Same.
Thanks to you.
Oh hey, thank you so mu...
Are you ok? You don't look so good.
Oh, it's just you, Miura.
You're looking really pale there.
Here's water?
Thank you.
Isn't Miura a nice girl?
Yukinon, are you okay?
Don't worry I'm fine.
It's just crowded... Plus a little hard to handle.
Let's go.
Yeah!
You know... This isn't very Christmas-like either.
Hurry up, Hikki!
Enjoy your trip into the world of...
Bamboo Fight!
Wow. This is amazing.
Quiet.
Really?
No talking allowed?
How much do you need to focus?
Aren't Mr. Pan's eyes really freakin' weird?
I mean, honestly... I'd rather
just look at Mary the Aristocat.
Really?
I actually think he's really super cute!
Isn't that right, Hayama?
Can't you see... She's trying to make herself
look cute and sweet by fawning over the panda?
Hi-ya!
Hey... Hey...
Annoying! Cute! Bothersome! Embarrassing!
Come on you can tell Mr. Pan what
is it that you really want, Hikki.
I don't really wa...
Nothing.. Really.
Oh, sure okay.
It's really crowded, huh?
I'm surprised they wanted to come at this time of year.
I'll never come again, if I can help it.
I would... I'd want to come
again if I ever got the chance...
You can come back anytime.
It's close.
That's not really...
what I meant though.
However I won't wait if there's no point in waiting.
Instead of waiting.. I'll move first.
Destinyland is really bad at this time of the year.
But I really wouldn't mind knowing what
the newer park next door is like you know.
I bet you it it's a bit quieter there... Maybe.
Maybe.
Well..someday then.
Mm..someday then.
Let's choose something... shall we?
Hikki! How about these?
So, um.. Which one of these would Komachi like?
Lighten up you don't have to
be so serious here of all places.
Hey, Yukinon.
What?
Hikki! Can you take a picture?
Oh yeah... Okay. Got it.
What? Really?
Uh... Are you okay?
Yes.
Oh no!
It's okay. We'll catch up later.
Okay then!
Shall we go?
Great idea.
She's not answering.
Since we've gotten this far,
we may as well enjoy the ride.
They might be waiting for us at the exit.
R... Right, yes.
Wait a second.. Are you scared of these rides?
Not exactly... I mean I'm not scared, but...
You really should've said
something earlier. Let's go back.
It'll be okay.
But, you don't like these rides, right?
I'm saying it's going to be okay.
Are you crazy?
This isn't something worth getting stubborn about.
That's not it.
It'll be fine, really.
So..I wasn't really sure at first,
but when I rode with Yuigahama earlier, I was fine.
I think I can handle this... Most likely.
The drop isn't happening soon,
so you can let go of the bar.
O-..okay then.
You really aren't good with these, are you?
I'm not.
It's because of my sister, really.
When we were kids...
She'd always manage to find some way
to mess with me at places like this.
I can see that happening.
She looked like she was having fun...
No matter what she was doing.
That's how she's always been.
Hey, Hikigaya...
Promise me.. You'll save me someday.
Here.
Thank you.
How much was it?
Don't worry.
There's no way I'm taking money from someone who's sick.
That's not a good reason.
Ambulances don't ask for money.
But Paramedics need to get paid for their services...
We've gotten into a similar argument before.
Huh, did we?
It was after we got that doll.
Oh yeah that.
We ran into my sister after that.
You know what... I must admit I was
surprised when you saw through her.
That was just the impression I got from her.
Besides, she doesn't cover things
up when people can see through her.
You're right.
I think that's part of her charm actually.
She just has this thing. Everyone always loves her.
As for me.. I was the obedient girl
that never gave anyone any trouble,
People talked... called me stuck-up,
unpleasant... and other things behind my back.
Yeah... You know.. I got that as well.
However, in your case.. It was probably
things more like crass, cheeky, or trash.
Whoa. Wasn't the last one pretty uncalled for?
So anyways... I had no idea how I was supposed to act.
So are you still wishing to be more like your big sister?
I don't know. I don't really feel that way anymore...
though she does have something
about her that I definitely don't have.
And you feel like you need that?
No. I used to sit and wonder why I didn't
have what she did but... it would just upset me.
You have it too.
You also have something that I don't have either.
So really, we weren't similar at all.
Guess you're right.
I think... I wanted something different.
And when I finally realized I
couldn't do much of anything,
I started wanting something that neither one of you had.
I thought if I had that, I could help.
Help what?
Huh... I wonder?
I'm sorry we went on without you!
Don't worry its no big deal.
I hope you got some real good pictures
at the parade while we were gone.
Yeah! I got some of Mr. Pan, too.
Oh let me see that, do you mind if
I take a look at all your pictures.
You know you could have gone too if you'd said something.
Hey? Where's Hayato?
Hey Yumiko, let's go over here.
Hey wait. What are you doing, Tobe?
Just come with me.
It's starting.
Brings back memories, huh?
I-Iroha?
Iroha!
"Of all who give gifts, these two were the most wise".
"Everywhere they are the wise ones."
That's the "Gift of the Magi."
Seriously?
They should've just talked it out as a married couple.
I think they're going to break
up due to lack of communication.
You're so ruthless, Rumirumi.
Calling me Rumirumi is gross.
G-Gross?
I dare you to say that one more time... Please.
Gross.
O-One more, no, three more times!
You're all so dumb.