So... See ya.
There's just one week left before
the big Christmas event, right?
I went to see how things were
going, but everyone had already left.
I was on my way home from the mall when
I looked over and saw you sitting there.
Oh.
Is this your car, Ms. Hiratsuka?
You had a different one during the summer didn't you?
Yeah... that was just a rental car for camp.
This one's my baby.
Hikigaya...
Do you mind if we make a quick stop?
Here we are.
Hikigaya.
You know... You look pretty cool there.
It's because I'm acting really cool.
So tell me.. How's it going?
It's going pretty bad.
Oh? What's bad about it?
Tough question. I don't know if I
can give a short answer for that one.
Come on.. Just give it a try.
'Kay...
Well...
I guess the big problem is our timing.
We just have one week left...
And I don't know how to solve the situation we're in.
Tamanawa and Isshiki.. They're both really scared.
They don't want to be blamed for things that may go wrong,
so to avoid taking responsibility, they just go about
gathering everyone's opinions and accepting them all.
The result of that.. Is this
current stagnant situation we're in.
Where it's not clear on who's supposed to be
leading, and who is shouldering the most responsibility.
That was our first mistake.
Well I guess it's something along those lines.
You look closely...
And you really excel at figuring
out what people are thinking.
That's not true...
However,
you just don't understand their feelings.
People's thoughts and emotions aren't always the same...
That's why they sometimes seem to come to
completely irrational conclusions that confuse us.
That's also why Yukinoshita, Yuigahama,
and you yourself, give the wrong answers.
Wait... Those two are not involved
with the project I'm currently working on.
Well actually.. I was asking about
those two from the start, Hikigaya.
But I guess... Both of them are the same inside...
Which means there's one thing at the root of this:
It's the heart.
Maybe but that's not really something I
can just think about and understand... is it?
You just don't get it, huh?
Well then.. Think about it some more.
Keep calculating until there's nothing left.
Think up all the answers, then squash them one by one,
and then what's left.. Is your answer.
Yea but still... Doesn't mean that
it'll help me understand any better?
Okay... then your calculations are
wrong.. Or you've missed something.
So you should do your calculations again.
You're crazy, you know that?
And you're an idiot!
If you could calculate feelings,
we'd have them on hard drives by now.
The last answer, the one you're unable to solve.
That's what we call human emotions.
I know... I also make those kind of mistakes
when I do my own calculating, which
is probably why I'm still on the market.
Just the other day, one of my friends got married...
See... That's because nobody's got good taste in women.
Huh?
If I had been born ten years earlier,
and if we had met ten years ago,
I think that maybe I would have fallen for her hard.
It means nothing to think about that now, though.
Whaa... Where did that come from?
Well.. Okay then.
As a way of thanking you for that..
I'm going to give you a special hint here.
When you sit and think...
You need to figure out and make
sure you focus on the right point.
For example,
think about why you are helping Isshiki,
not as a member of the service club, but by yourself.
Try to think about why you did that.
Was this for the service club.. Or for Yukinoshita?
I could tell just by looking.
After the election issue..
Yukinoshita came to me about it.
You know she doesn't really talk about herself..
But I could tell how she felt by the way she was acting.
Are you the same way in that regard?
Uh.. Well. I don't really know.
Well if you hold anywhere near
the same beliefs that she does..
Then you wind up thinking that in order to not
hurt those you care for, you must push them away.
In my opinion anyway.
Of course it's all hypothetical.
Yeah, I guess so.
In a hypothetical situation.
However, that's not what you should be thinking about.
For instance.. You should really stop and think
expressly about why you don't want to hurt them.
And you should have that answer immediately.
They have become important to you...
So you do not wish to hurt them.
But, you know, Hikigaya...
It's impossible to never hurt anyone.
Simply just by existing... We'll
unconsciously manage to hurt someone.
They do it when they are living, and
even still do it after they've died.
They do it by getting involved... Even if they
try not to get involved, they'll still hurt someone.
However when it's someone you don't care about,
you won't even notice if you hurt them.
What's necessary is self-awareness.
When you feel like you're hurting
someone... It proves that you care about them.
That's what caring for people is about.
You must be prepared to hurt that
person even when you try not to.
That's my hint for you.
Sometimes people will lose out on things, because
they're thinking about protecting someone else.
But... That isn't something you should be sad about.
Maybe, it's something you should be proud of.
I don't know, that all sounds so hard.
Yeah. It can be hard.
You can do it. Because I was able to do it.
Maybe so... But assuming people can do what you can..
Is a little presumptuous.
Seriously, you are such a brat!
Okay, then.
I'll be honest.
You know... It might not even have to be you that does it.
Someday in the future...
Yukinoshita herself may change.
Maybe someone that can even
understand her will appear before her.
Or there might be someone who
will come and break down her walls.
That's also true... of Yuigahama as well.
Maybe.. Someday huh?
To all you guys, the present feels
like it's the most important thing ever.
But that is in no way true.
You can always balance things out eventually.
That's how the world works after all.
However,
That said, I think it would be nice if it were you.
I have hope that you and Yuigahama will
get in and break down Yukinoshita's walls.
Well...
Easier said then done... As you know.
Remember the present isn't everything...
But... there are things you can do
now... that can only be found here.
And the time is now.
It's right now.
Just keep on thinking and
struggling. Flounder in your distress.
If you don't do that, it isn't genuine.
Yea but...
It doesn't mean you're being
genuine just because you're struggling.
Oh wow you really are a royal brat, aren't you?
My current obstacle is of course the big
joint Christmas event that's looming over us.
And with that, Iroha Isshiki's issue has reared its head.
And everything is entangled in Rumi Tsurumi's situation.
What is the most suitable solution to these problems?
I don't think I can fix this alone.
Should I ask for help? Why am I
trying to lean on others so soon?
The bonds between people are like some types of drugs.
Before you know it, you've become dependent on them.
During the student council
election, Komachi was my reason.
"Do it for Komachi."
That was my excuse to act.
No..I had to do this my way.
I was probably wrong at the
time... and most likely still am.
I need to act based on the answer,
the reason that I find for myself.
Yukinoshita and Yuigahama...
Why didn't I want to let those two run for president?
Until I got a reason...
My real reason to act was...
Because there was something I wanted.
Come in.
Hikki.
Something wrong? You actually knocked and all...
I said you don't have to force yourself to show up.
But I'm here for a reason now.
Have a seat.
What's going on?
You're acting a little different than normal.
I've come to make a request.
A request? You're actually going to speak to us now?
You know the Christmas event Isshiki came to us about?
It's way more difficult than I thought.
So I'd like to ask for your help.
Yea but...
No.. I know what you want to say.
I took it all upon myself..
And I said it wouldn't help Isshiki in the end.
But I'm the one that advised her
to be student council president.
Do you remember the students at camp this summer?
That girl is participating.. But it's like before.
I do.. Her name is Rumi, right?
See, I really want to do something.
I know because of what I've done,
I've caused all these problems.
And by coming here I'm being selfish...
Wanting your help. Needing it.
So that means... you admit to this being your fault?
Yeah.. I can't deny it.
Right.
Since you are responsible for all of this by yourself...
Then you should also be able to solve it all by yourself.
Right.
My bad... Forget I asked.
Wait.
It's not like that...
It doesn't have to be! This is wrong!
She's right. I should fix it myself.
It's perfectly natural to do
that. I need clean up after myself.
It is.
It's not!
Both of you are totally wrong about all this!
Look.. You aren't the only one responsible here.
You might've thought of the idea...
And you might have even carried it out..
But we're no better in this either!
We forced all of this on you.
No.. That's not really true here.
Yes, it is!
It's not just your fault..
Things HAVE gotten weird around here..
And I'm just as.. Responsible to...
I...
Yukinon what you said just now... Is unfair in my opinion.
Now you're going to go and say that?
You are a coward as well.
Wait.. This is not what I want
to talk about, nor why I came here.
Yukinon.. You've said nothing.
There are things that you have to
tell us, or we won't ever get it.
You never said anything either.
From the beginning you've acted
as if nothing was the matter.
I thought.. That you-
that's how you both wanted things to be... then...
"There are things that you have
to tell us, or we won't get it."
But then... There are things that
we won't get even if you do say it.
That's not what I...
Maybe I can't... Maybe I can't
accept it, even if you say it out loud.
I'd probably think there's some other
reason for it, or some sort of ulterior motive.
Or some other selfish reason for telling me.
But, if..
If we actually talk about it...
And have conversations... Then we...
But that's not it.
It's arrogant to think something
like that would be understood.
The pretension of the person who said it...
And conceit of the person it was told to...
There are many things that you won't
absolutely understand if you just talk about it.
That's why... I don't just want words.
That's not true...
If nobody says something, then how can you understand!
Yeah... Expecting people to
understand without words is delusional.
But...
But I...
I...
I just...
I don't only want words.
There was certainly something that I wanted all along.
Not understanding each other, becoming good friends, being
together, sharing together... Or anything else like that.
I don't need to be understood.
I want to understand.
To understand. To know.
I want to know and have peace. I want to be at ease.
Because the things that I don't know are frickin' scary.
Wanting to understand completely is a terribly
self-righteous, tyrannical, arrogant desire.
It's really disgraceful and nauseating.
Holding that desire is so disgusting I can't stand it!
But, if...
If, we can both share that desire,
if we can burden each other
with that ugly self-satisfaction...
and if we can allow that relationship to exist...
I know that that relationship is completely impossible!
I know that type of thing is not within my reach!
And yet-
And yet, I find...
I...
I really...
want something genuine.
Oh Hikki...
I don't.. Really understand.
I'm sorry.
Yukinon!
Hikki!
Let's go!
No way.. I'm not going.
Yes you are, we're gonna go together!
Yukinon said she didn't understand...
I also think she doesn't know
what to do in this type of situation,
and come to think of it I don't know either. But..
We can't let whatever we have end without knowing!
Now or never!
This is the first time I've seen Yukinon like this!
Come on.. We have to go after her...
I can walk on my own fine.
Let's go.
U..Um hey..
I was going to come in but you seem to be in a hurry...
We really are.
We gotta go.
Uh... there's no meeting today. Wanted you to know.
A-And uh...
Okay.. Got it.
Wait...
Please just stop and listen to me for a second...
If you're looking for her she's upstairs. Go!
Thanks for that.
Yukinon!
I don't understand it.
I don't get what you mean by "genuine?" I'm confused.
That's why...
It's okay.. Yukinon.
What do you mean it's okay?
If we're being honest here.. I
didn't really understand myself.
So... if we talk about it, we'll understand it better...
But... Maybe even then we won't understand, right?
And that's fine.. We may never
really come to understand it.. I mean...
I can totally see us not ever being able to get it.
So maybe I don't understand after all.
But, you know...
I really...
Seriously.. Hate the way things are right now!
Hey now.. Why are you crying?
I really was right, huh?
Coward.
Hikigaya.
Yeah?
As for your request... I accept.
Thank you
im gonna help, too.
I appreciate it.
Beer is the best!
It was so not me, delivering that cool speech.
Way to go, me! I'm a great teacher!
No, a great woman.
Why can't a great woman like me get married?
'Scuse me! Can I get a chicken
wasabi? And a husband while you're at it!
Just kidding!
Ugh, it's almost Christmas.
Makes me sick. If only I didn't have to work.
If I didn't have to work, I
could party all through Christmas!
Can I get a highball, please!
I wanna get married.