Hey...
Did something happen?
Nothing I can recall.
I would say if anything...
there's so little happening it's like watching grass grow.
They say "Inscrutable are the ways of Heaven,"
but it would probably go better if
it said "Sometimes things just happen."
What's going on, Big Bro?
Uh... let's see...
Nope, nothing's up at all.
I think I know.
Know what? The muffin man?
You always just sit there and
try to tell me nothing is going on,
but you say that even more when you aren't doing so well.
Oh, really?
Big Brother...?
Hm?
Did something happen with Yukino and Yui?
Did they come and say something to you?
I just thought that might be the problem.
Really...
Well then... did you do something?
The assumption that I did something is simply ridiculous.
Even if you aren't aware of it there's
still a high probability that you did something.
You have no choice.
You've gotta tell me everything now.
That's easier said than done.
It's really nothing.
Oh, come on!
Just tell me what happened okay?
God, you're persistent.
Just back off.
What?! Why are you talking like that to me?
I just said what I usually say.
Which is, you were being to persistent and annoying.
Fine.
Forget I asked.
That's fine by me.
I'm leaving, so make sure you lock the door.
Okay.
I know something happened!
Morning!
Is this the world that wants to
always keep things just the way they are?
Morning, Hachiman.
Yea... morning.
Huh?
Hm? What is it?
It's nothing really.
I was just thinking how normal your greeting was.
Yeah... I guess, you're right, huh?
It's normal.
So bitter.
And did you know that the crepe shop
by the station is actually really good?
Really?
We should go sometime, Yukinon!
Chocolate banana is the...
So you came.
Yeah I guess so.
Hey... by the way, everyone was normal today.
You know... I mean... everyone...
That's true.
Just looking at them, it was like nothing had happened.
If it's true, then that's good.
You're right... but I was totally on pins and needles.
I guess it really wasn't something
I needed to worry about was it!
It was all... completely... normal.
I just don't understand what they're all thinking anymore.
No one does... from the start we had no real idea.
There was no way for us to know...
Even if we know each other...
understanding one another is a totally different problem.
I wouldn't really worry about it too much.
I also think it'd be best if we just went back to normal.
We should go back to normal.
Yeah.
Normal... huh.
Huh...
Right... so I suppose that is
what you're considering normal then.
So you're saying... you're not going to change?
You are just... uh...
I...
Yukinon!
Uh... So, um...
Come on.
Just me, coming in!
I want to ask a favor of you guys.
Hmh... Did something happen here?
Nope, nothing. So, did you need something from us?
Right! You can come in!
There's something I want to get your help with...
Oh, Shiromeguri...
Oh, hey there, Iroha!
Hey Yui! Hi everyone!
Yahallo! Long time no see!
Wow so you're a candidate for student council president?
Yes.
Um... I bet you think that I'm not
really cut out to be the president, huh?
Uh, no, not really...
I know people say all sorts of things about me.
Like I seem kind of dumb or slow.
So then, what's the problem you're bringing us?
As you can see Isshiki is running
for student council president, but...
let's see, how should I go about saying this...
We want it so she doesn't get elected.
Hm...
So, um... you're saying that you don't
want to be the student council president?
Yes, that's right.
Then why are you even running for it?
Well, uh... I didn't exactly enter myself as a candidate.
Someone did it behind my back.
Huh? Is she a celebrity?
I would say that I'm pretty noticeable in a bad way.
It's like that... It does seem
like she'd be hated by other girls.
It was the same in junior high...
You already had boys wrapped around
your little finger, like a juggler.
Even as a joke, this is pretty complicated.
To become a candidate, you had to
be nominated by at least 30 people.
That many? You got a lot, huh?
I'll be talking to these students who did this, of course.
If you don't want to do it, then just drop out of it.
I mean, there's nothing else you can do.
Well... you see the problem is Isshiki
is the only candidate right now...
Then she needs a vote of no confidence, right?
But it would be so lame to lose an election
like that! There's no way I could do that.
Have you decided on who will give your campaign speech?
I haven't.
Great, this will be easy then.
Why's that? What do you mean?
Worst case scenario, if it
comes to a vote of no confidence,
we can lose the election and Isshiki will
be able to extract herself without any damage.
Which would be a good thing because then everyone would
know. Isshiki didn't cause herself to lose the election.
Can you do something like that?
No one will blame Isshiki if there is a lack of confidence
in her due to a poorly delivered campaign speech.
And who do you suppose we get to make that kind of speech?
Hm, Hikki?
I don't think... I like that.
It's best if...
Whoever is capable should be the one who goes up there.
Well I won't approve you doing it that way.
What's your reason?
Because...
it'd be too unreliable.
Moreover... a horrible speech that creates a lack
of confidence in Isshiki could cause her trouble.
Even if that created a lack of confidence, do
you think they would bother doing another election?
That's why...
interest in the student council is so low.
No one would care if they announced the
results without making the number of votes public.
So, see there could be any number...
Yukinoshita.
Slip of the tongue. I retract that.
Uh...
The only other method would be...
to put our support behind another candidate.
If someone else wanted to do it...
explain why they haven't already signed up to run?
I know, we could try to choose someone
that would go up there and do it for us...
Looks like we won't figure it out today.
Let's try again later.
Okay.
Ms. Hiratsuka.
Hm?
Can I please have a moment of your time?
Hm.
What do you think the outcome would be as of now?
Huh?
What outcome is that?
For a competition on who can better serve people...
and which of us can better solve someone's problems.
The winner orders the loser to do whatever they want.
Wait, this is what we're doing?
Th-that's correct.
There have been situations where
everyone worked together to solve a task.
On that front you're all doing well.
If you want to know where you three stand individually...
I guess I can tell you something
at my own discretion and bias.
That's fine.
Well if I were to only judge by the results, then..
Hikigaya is one step ahead.
But if I take into account the process and progress,
Yukinoshita is on top.
However, in either case, without Yuigahama's
contributions this would be impossible...
So then... the match isn't decided yet.
That sounds about right.
I see... so that means even
though our opinions are different...
there's no problem, right?
I don't know what you mean by that?
I mean that it's not necessary.
We don't need to use the same methods.
Ah...
So then there's no real reason for us to
strain ourselves to make our opinions match.
Well then... what will the club do until this is resolved?
People can still participate.
That sounds reasonable.
Uh...
Remember, Hikigaya...
the thing you and I hate the most is being superficial.
Did something happen?
Nope.
Really...
Okay.
You know you're a nice guy, right?
You've helped quite a lot of people here.
Don't say that, it's not true.
I know it doesn't seem like
it, but I do show favoritism here.
Yeah how's that workin' out
with you being a teacher and all?
I praise and encourage all students.
You know I don't really buy that load of crap at all.
Why, because I also scold you?
Well going by your methods, when you meet
someone that you actually want to help...
you're not gonna be able to help them.
Thank you for your business!
That's not a face I see very often.
Don't just up and run away from me. That's rude of you.
Hikigaya.
Yes.
Why don't you tell me something interesting?
Just look at that super hateful reaction!
Yea, just as I expected!
So... is Yukino doing okay?
Well, she isn't any different than usual.
Really... that's great then.
So... has there been any progress?
What?
Didn't you go on the school trip?
You sure are in the know.
The souvenirs arrived at the house.
She used a delivery service?
She probably didn't want to see me.
And yet she still bought you all souvenirs.
She's loyal.
Maybe... but I don't think that's really the case.
Huh?
She actually hates us... but she doesn't want to be hated.
So now that the big events seem to be all over with...
all that's left are the entrance exams huh?
Don't you find that boring?
No, not really.
Don't forget there are also still the
student council elections and whatnot.
Oh right...
So Meguri's finally retiring her role, huh?
She is Meguri after all. Did she request for
you to make Yukino the student council president?
Uh, no, she actually didn't.
What? That's boring.
So Yukino won't become the student council president?
Probably not.
Hmm...
Um... what about it?
Hmh? Well... I didn't do it either, I guess.
That's pretty boring.
Uh...
Huh? Hikigaya?
Whoa, I haven't seen you in forever!
What a rare encounter to have.
Orimoto...?
I really thought junior high school classmates had
been thrown out of the innermost recesses of my memories.
But Kaori Orimoto's name had easily come to me.
Wait...
You go to Soubu High School, right?
Uh... I do.
Oh, so you're really smart then, huh?
I didn't know that.
I mean, it's not like you
really talked to anyone back then.
Uh?
This your girlfriend?
No, she's not...
Of course not. I knew that'd be pretty impossible.
I'm forcing a smile, this is gross.
This girl is actually one of your friends?
Am I imagining it, or did that sound more like,
"Did you really have friends?"
She's an old junior high school classmate.
I'm Kaori Orimoto.
Hmm...
Hi... My name is Haruno Yukinoshita..
I'm Hikigaya's...
Hey...
Hm?
Well, what would you say we are, Hikigaya?
Uh... I don't think I really know.
It'd be weird to tell people
that we're actually "friends".
Maybe more like a big sister...
I know! How about we just tell them I'm your girlfriend?
How about we just plainly say
that you're an alum from school?
You're so coldhearted to me!
So you two went to the same school together, huh?
You have any interesting stories?
Huh?
Oh, a love story?!
I want to hear all about young Hikigaya's love life.
Uh... now that you mention it.
Hikigaya did ask me out once in junior high!
No way!
I so have to hear that!
I was so surprised because we
hadn't talked at all until then.
We had talked...
We texted each other.
We traded addresses out of pity or compassion...
I used all sorts of trivial reasons to text her,
and waited to see if a text would ever come or not...
But I bet she didn't know or even
remember that those things were happening.
Wow, Hikigaya asked you out, huh?
Well, it was a really long time ago.
Yeah, it was a long time ago
and it doesn't really matter now.
O-oh yeah!
You know a guy named Hayama at Soubu?
Hm? Uh... more or less.
For real?!
Chika, he can introduce you to Hayama!
Huh? Uh, no thanks.
No, he's not really a friend.
Yeah... I guess you're right.
I can see that not happening.
Hmm, this seems like fun...
Hi... Big Sis will introduce you to him!
Huh?
Hey Hayato? Are you able to come out now?
Or rather, just come.
We're at the donut shop near the station.
What do you think you're doing right now?
Bye, Hayama! I'll send you a text later, okay?!
Holy crap. He was so cool.
Why did you do that Haruno?
Because it seemed like such fun.
Not that again?
And I don't get why Hikigaya's here too?
He has nothing to do with this does he?
That's not true!
Hikigaya actually liked the girl with
the perm back in his junior high days.
I wonder what kind of face Yukino would make if she knew?
Well, that was a good way to waste some time tonight.
I guess I will head out now guys.
Thanks for hanging out with me, Hikigaya.
Bye now.
It looks like Haruno has taken a liking to you.
Huh? Are you stupid?
She's just making fun of me.
She doesn't poke her nose into the
business of people she has no interest in.
She wouldn't do anything.
She just smothers and kills the things she likes...
or thoroughly crush the things that she hates.
That's scary.
Huh?
Good morning there!
Hey.
Are you planning on going to the club room today?
Nope, I'm not.
Oh.. Okay, then.
Um...
We thought that we should talk to
Iroha a bit more this afternoon...
and it seems like we'll decide on a strategy.
I didn't... I didn't want you to think we
were doing anything without you knowing about it.
Well, if it's just to listen then I'll come.
I wonder how long it's been
since I've openly opposed Yukino.
It's the same now, too.
Yukinoshita will reject my method of doing things,
but if it's the same, there is no problem.
You actually really came!
Then let us begin now.
It seems like the best option is
for us to find another candidate...
then as their running opposite to you,
you'll now have the chance to lose
peacefully against them in a run-off.
I think you're right about that.
But personally, I think it would be good
if I could lose against an awesome person.
I thought about the contents of the commitment
pledge and campaign speech for the candidate.
When you say you thought of a commitment pledge,
you mean the candidate would be a total puppet.
But is that really okay?
If that person is elected, then what will
you do about managing the student council?
So then we just have to make sure to
find someone who can do the job properly.
The hurdle has been raised even more.
If we're thinking about the future then there's no point,
plus it's not a very clever move.
Then... what is the point to your method?
In this scenario, she can avoid the worst
outcome and when she loses the vote of no confidence,
she can then drop out of the re-election process...
"In this scenario..."?
No. You're wrong.
You always go avoiding the problem like this.
So what? Did it cause any problems?
Earlier didn't you call this
type of superficiality meaningless?
You really don't want to change?
No.
B-but, hey..
Um...
I'm heading home.
Hey!
I wonder if this will be okay.
I mean I would feel a lot better if
a good person ran against me, but...
So then someone like Hayama would be good.
No way, it can't be Hayama!
If worse comes to worst, I'll fix it.
Thanks so much!
No one really wants to help me.
I can only depend on you guys in the Service Club.
Oh!
I have got to get to practice now.
Well, I'm counting on you!