So tell me... how's this your "go to" solution?
See... it's easy.
I've made a world where no one gets hurt.
The culture festival and the athletic
festival ended with no huge mistakes,
and in the blink of an eye the
collective school temperature dropped,
and a cold wind blew.
Furthermore... my surroundings are even bleaker.
But it's always like that.
Hey, bro!
Why're you're leaving me out? What
am I Hikitani? Or is it Whatatani!
Yeah Yeah, very funny.
By the way, my name from the
beginning has never been Hikitani.
Yahello!
Huh... Oh.
You'll be at service club today, right?
Yeah.
Okay. See you in the club room.
Hachiman!
Hm?
We need to pick our group for the Kyoto trip... our
teacher said we can do it during our homeroom class.
Really? Seems like everyone
has already made up their groups.
You really think so?
Because I haven't found a group to join yet...
Uh...
I want to protect that smile!
Would you like to be in a group together then?
Mm...
Hey!
Hellooo!
Hey, where'd ya go Hayato?
Are you becoming a loner like Whatatani?
Can't I go to the bathroom by myself.
By the way, Tobe, you're using that joke way too often.
Joke about him too much and you'll sink to his level...
you need TO BE better than him.
OH... so now it's about me! Cut me some slack, man!
Thanks!
Your tea's going to get cold.
Huh?
My mouth burns easily.
I wish our school had picked somewhere
more exciting for our trip, like Okinawa.
Kyoto is pretty lame isn't it?
Actually there is quite a lot to do in Kyoto.
We can see and experience this
country's culture first hand.
I don't think that's why we're really going.
Really? Then why do you suppose they
make us go on these overnight school trips?
They're giving us an imitation of society.
When you go on a business trip with your boss, you don't
get to choose where you stay or even what's for dinner.
But if you compromise, it can be fun in its own way, it's
like practice for deceiving yourself in the future really.
Your school trip doesn't sound
like it's very much fun, Hikki.
Come on surely even someone like you has to have
one or two things you're looking forward to seeing?
Maybe.
Like bathing with Saika...
Well, I haven't had a chance
to look up anything about it yet.
Have you, Yukinon?
Well, let's see.
There's Ryoan-ji, and Kiyomizudera temples...
but I would also really like to go and see
the famous places around Rokuon-ji and Jishou.
Rokuonjishouji...
Don't mix them up.
They do kinda sound like pretty
cool character names though.
Sorry to have gone and confused you two,
their more common known names
are Kinkaku-ji and Ginkaku-ji.
So why didn't you say that in the first place?
And I guess...
that's about it.
You know a lot!
What are you, a travel book or something?
She's way too excited about this.
Having knowledge about Kyoto is
just general knowledge, isn't it?
Hm?
What is it?
Oh it's nothing, nothing here to see at all!
Come in.
Hey!
Can we help you?
He needs a consult about
something. So I brought him to you.
Ah, it's nothing I mean nothing
I need to talk to Hikitani about.
We came to ask for a favor, right?
But I can't talk to him... not about this kind of
thing, his reliability is less than zero at this point!
Jerk...
You can't just walk into our room and say that.
Well, it IS Hikigaya's fault, so it
can't be helped. He's just like that.
I'm sorry...
I'll need to ask you to leave the room now.
That's fine, just let me know
when you guys are done in here.
Where you going? Just sit back down.
They're the ones who are leaving.
They don't have manners or understand politeness.
There is no need to listen to them or to
their rude pleas for our help at this time.
I'm going to kindly ask you guys to please leave us again.
Yeah, you guys are really annoying.
Ah... we're very sorry.
Let's go now, Tobe. We can figure it out on our own.
I'm sorry but we can't go, we just gotta do this.
Um... actually, I just...
What!
So basically... you wanna confess
to Ebina and ask her out, correct?
Yeah, that's exactly right!
But she'll probably just give me the cold shoulder.
Ah... you don't wanna be rejected.
This is gonna be so fun and super exciting!
You've got this!
I don't think it's really all that easy.
You may be right...
Honestly... I don't think we'd be useful.
What? It's okay... we can help him!
Please?
What... don't try to force this decision on me.
Hikitani... please...
Hikitani... Please, man!
No, no, no. You're being too polite in
asking me... you're not really meaning it...
And you're still getting my name wrong.
Please Yukinon, Tobecchi's
looks pretty troubled about this.
If you really think he looks that
troubled, then I guess I'll think on it.
Hey Yukinoshita, you've really
been spoiling Yuigahama lately.
Okay, we'll do it.
And what should we do, specifically?
Well, I... I'll just come right out and ask you...
could you be my moral support?
Perfect!
I suppose we can understand your feelings on this.
However, this could be a bit risky for you.
What do you mean risky?
Risky. The danger or the possibility of suffering a loss.
I know what "risk" means Yukinon,
what I meant was what kind of risk.
First he confesses, then she rejects him.
So you already know she'll do that?
But not only that.
The next day, it's natural that everyone
in the class will know, as well, right?
It's okay if they know. But then you
start to hear them talking about you.
So it seems like creepy Hikigaya confessed to Kaori!
Whoa, poor Kaori! I'm glad I
didn't tell him my email address!
You'll be made the subject of everyone's gossip...
and there's a tiny risk you'll get hurt.
Wait was that another one of your stories...
Believe me there are others.
For example, if you confess to one of your
good friends, your relationship after that is...
Okay, okay, we get it.
We'll be really careful on that front.
Well, gotta go to club practice.
Okay, well for now, let's start
with some of Tobe's charming points.
I'm friends with Hayato!
You're immediately depending on others!
Surely you've got something else?
How about... he's always cheerful?
If it were that easy, then bald people would be popular.
Yukinoshita?
Let's see...
Annoying... no that doesn't work, what about loud?
Or how about noisy...
Or maybe lively will work. What do you think?
Okay, I got it.
Change of plans.
So fast!?
Yes, instead of looking for Tobe's good
points, we'll change him into Ebina's type.
Oh, I see!
There's something else. We should figure
out what Ebina's thoughts are about Tobe?
Huh?
Yea... I wonder that too.
Oh, well that seems to be obvious.
Yeah... me too... I really
wanna know what she thinks of me!
You sure about that?
This is the final judgment, there's no turning back.
Well, if we don't know we can't
really move forward with this, right?
Alright... Let's hear it.
Well I think.. She believes you're just a really good guy.
Oh, that's unfortunate.
When girls say "a good guy" it 100% means "I don't care."
Wow... that's a good thing, isn't it?
Your thinking is the only good thing.
I've got it!
Exploring Kyoto will be a great
time to put this into action.
If I remember correctly Hina said she likes Kyoto.
If that's the case...
we have to make a situation where
Tobe and Ebina are together alone.
I wonder if we can make that work.
Come in.
Excuse me!
Oh, it's Hina!
Hey there, Yui! Hello Hello!
Oh... Ya hallo!
Huh, what is that? Some sort of tribal greeting?
And Hello hello, Yukinoshita and Hikitani!
Hey.
Why don't you please come in and join us.
What's up?
Um, well...
It's about Tobecchi...
I've got a bit of an issue.
You mean with Tobecchi? What is it?
Well... Tobecchi is...
Tobecchi is what?
Lately...
it seems as if Tobecchi is getting
really close to Hayato and Hikitani!
Which means Ooka and Yamato are getting sooo frustrated!
I want to see them indulge into their relationships more!
But with this new angle, the
love triangle will be spoiled!
Well that's...
Don't you think Tobecchi's been
talking with Hikitani a lot recently?
They keep sending meaningful glances to each other.
If you're going to invite more people
in, then you should invite everyone.
And also be more accepting of them.
Actually, I want you to be inviting and accepting.
No way. Never.
Tell us what you're actually trying to say?
Maybe it's weird, but to me it feels like
the group dynamic has changed a bit lately...
Maybe. But just remember that males also have
complicated things happening in their lives too,
such as in their relationships.
Ew, complicated male relationships...
That's so unlady like...
Did I say just something awkward?
No, you just summed it all up. It's okay.
Our group dynamic was certainly different in the past.
It just feels so weird now.
I just wish we'd get along like we use to.
Oh before I forget, I also think it
would be great if we got along with Hikitani.
It'd be such a feast for my eyes!
So for our upcoming school trip...
I'm really looking forward to some great memories!
Don't forget... invite people in!
Thanks, Hikitani, I'll see you guys later!
I wonder what that was about...
I'm not sure...
But maybe she's trying to make it
so that everyone gets along again.
Oh, you think so? But, um, Hikki...
How do you guys get along with each other anyway?
Don't you think that asking Hikigaya
that sort of question is quite cruel?
Really Yuigahama, try to be a little more thoughtful.
'Kay?
Really. Think about my feelings a little more!
Hmm...
So how do you guys think we should pick our seats?
Can't we just sit wherever?
Ooh, I want the window seat.
Thank you, Hayato!
You two can sit next to me!
So, Hina will sit here, and
Tobecchi can sit next to her...
Hey, you sit here, Yui.
And I'll be here. And Kawasaki will be across from me.
No... no, it's ok I'll sit somewhere else!
No! It's okay.
So where do you think we should go sit?
Stop it.. Hachi... Hachiman...
Hey... this is getting to be difficult.
What did something happen over there?
All sorts of things...
Kawasaki's been scaring Tobecchi this whole time,
so the conversation isn't going anywhere.
Hina is much more... Hina than usual.
What a disaster for Tobe.
I wish there was a way for
them to be alone with each other.
But if only those two were there
together, maybe nothing would happen.
You might be right.
Oh, Tobe...
Oh no, you heard that Saika?
It's no big deal I also heard it
on our camping trip over summer.
Right, Hachiman?
Yeah.
I have a confession...
I think... I might actually like Ebina.
Ah!
Mount Fuji! Look, over there!
So close!
Ah, I want to see too.
Wow. Mount Fuji is just so beautiful!
That type of innocent behavior... So many
boys misunderstand, resulting in certain death.
If you understand, commit and
say, "I won't make physical contact",
"I won't sit on a boy's seat during break", and
"If I forget something, I won't borrow it from a boy."
What're you doing...
Oh, sorry! I'm going go back over to my seat now.
Um, Hachiman...
Your arm, do you mind?
Uh... Sorry! Sorry!
Hikki!
Can I talk to you?
We'll talk later.
Did you forget your job already?
Look, I've already called Tobecchi and Hina.
Come on, hurry up!
It's so dark inside.
If I time it just right and we come in
from this side, they should end up alone.
'Kay.
I think we should all go in pairs!
Yumiko and Hayato will go first, and
then Hikki and I will follow up last.
I don't think we have much time left.. So
we shouldn't leave too much space between us.
I suppose you're right.
I really don't think this will take very long, yeah?
I wouldn't worry about it!
Right! I guess we don't really
need to get back early do we?
Hm?
Let's just go really quick, Hayato,
it looks like it'll be a lot of fun!
Well... we'll just go ahead of you guys.
Hm.
Whoa, it's really dark in here!
Seriously, though... this is MAXIMUM darkness here!
Isn't it?
It says we turn the rock and then we make a wish.
Okay.
Do you already know what to wish for?
I do.
'Kay, let's turn it together.
So that's what you do at a shrine.
Are you done?
Yeah.
Alright let's get out of here then.
Aww. I got "bad luck".
Yea but, that's okay!
Things can only get better
from here, so it's a good thing!
You think?
Hey...
Huh?
Offer to tie it up and be sure that you
do it in a higher place, that'd be better.
Oh?
Wait. Can I tie it up for you?
Oh.
Thank you! You're such a gentleman.
It seems that he's really trying to do
his best even if we don't do anything.
Wouldn't it be great, if it keeps going well like this?
Yeah.
I wonder if everyone here is aiming for luck in love.
Uh... yeah.
What are you doing?
Wow, this is really quite yummy.
Here, Hikki.
Oh man no way...
Uh, thanks but no thanks... it's
had other people's mouths on it.
Come on, seriously, that's not
something you should be worrying about.
I am worried about it.
Besides, if I drank from that I
wouldn't be able to focus on the taste.
There's no Max Coffee.
Hm?
Of course.
Night.
My, how unexpected.
Should've said that earlier when you saw me.
What's wrong? You leave because
your room was hard to be in?
If it was that hard for me, I
wouldn't have come in the first place.
And you?
I became the subject of my classmate's
gossip, so I decided to come here.
I don't understand why they like that kind of talk.
But if they're talking about you,
don't they want to get to know you?
What if you tried?
Well that's great advice coming from you...
considering at the cultural festival you-
Me? Wait...
No... It's not my fault, it's society's fault.
And? What's the status of our request?
It's not going well, but not badly either.
I'm sorry. Since I'm in another class I
can't really help with this assignment.
Don't worry about it.
Even though I'm in the same class, I'm not doing much.
Please work on that.
Huh?
Oh!
Yummm, that was so good!
It was ferociously flavorful.
That was specific.
But seriously, why did you take us out with you again?
Can a teacher really do that?
We're not supposed to.
So I decided to pay you some hush-money in ramen!
I would image that's even less appropriate for a teacher.
If you're caught, you'll be scolded.
Being scolded isn't necessarily a bad thing.
It's proof someone's looking out for you.
I'm always looking after you guys too.
So make all the mistakes you want.
Hm?
I'm going to go buy some party
supplies from the liquor store.
Bye now. Get back safely!
Take a right there.
O... oh.
Hey, if we get too far apart, you'll get lost again.
You can go on ahead of me.
It's not a big deal to stick together especially at night.
It's right there.
Maybe it's okay for you, but it's not for me.
And why not?
Well...
Cause it's this late at night and
we're together, and if we were seen out...
Yeah, you're right.
Bye.
Okay, good night.
And...
thanks for walking back with me.
When I get back, I'm gonna get in the bath with Saika.
Kyoto, huh?
Is there anywhere you want to go Hachiman?
Let's see. No matter where we go, we'll be together.
Or, as long as we're together anywhere
is fine! Oh, that's very Hachiman!
I want to go to Toei Kyoto Studio Park or Arashiyama.
A hot spring at Arashiyama would be nice...
What? Hot spring?!
S-Saika?
Hachiman...
Shut up, Zaimokuza. Be quiet.
Let's go together.
I want to protect this sleeping face!