Big bro!
Take this!
Hm?
Ta-da! It's my recommended souvenir list!
Read it, read it, read it, read it!
Number 3!
Raw yatsuhashi...?
I don't care where you get it, the
first store, the main store, anywhere!
Number 2!
You want oil-absorbing sheets?
Go ahead and get some for mom too, okay?
And now, the long-awaited Number 1!
So, are you going to tell me what's number 1?
The number 1 souvenir is...
My big bro's special memories from his trip!
She's cunning and cute...
Hachiman...!
Hachiman...
I never heard you say Uno!
Yaaay.
You're not even in this class.
Hayato!
Oh my god! I'm scared!
Oh man, oh man, oh man, oh man, oh man, oh man!
Did you hear that? A weird voice!
I seriously don't like this kind of stuff.
It's not the ghosts at a haunted house that are scary.
It's the living that are scary.
You can be such a sourpuss.
But you might be good for this type of thing.
Well the scariest haunted houses are the
ones where people are doing the scaring.
Forget it!
He's not good at this at all!
Hey... You seem completely fine with all this stuff.
Yeah, I actually like this type of thing.
Kawasaki?
Kawasaki!
Ouch!
Sorry!
Did I really hurt you?
Yeah, it really kind of hurt.
Well... nevermind, forget it.
Thank you.
Come on, let's go.
It's over...
That was really, really scary...
That was so much fun, wasn't it?!
Yeah.
We really had a good time in there, huh?
Should we head out soon?
Yea, let me go and look for Ebina.
Dude, a wooden sword!
Ebina, we're going!
Do you think the haunted house
actually worked at all on Tobe and Hina?
Hmm... I wonder.
Down we go.
What a coincidence.
You came here too?
Yes.
This place is known as "The Garden
of Tiger Cubs Crossing the Water."
Though I'm not sure which part are the tigers.
Oh. Of course, she's interested
since tigers are in the cat family.
She is a frisky cat lover.
Ah, Yukinon.
Let's go somewhere else ok.
How's the status of our request?
Um, it's a little difficult. Right?
We shouldn't push, or else Ebina will
start to suspect something and hate us.
And plus... We've got one person acting weird.
Plus what?
Nothing... just forget it.
I'm sorry that's it's been left up
to the two of you this whole time.
No, please don't worry about it.
But perhaps I can make up for it though.
I think that I've come up with
an idea to help you guys out.
What is it?
It's a list of places in Kyoto that girls might like.
It may be useful to them. Here.
Ah, that's my Yukinon!
Okay then, I'm going back.
'Kay. We will see you tomorrow then.
Great. See you guys tomorrow.
Hello, Hikkio.
So... what in the world are you guys trying to do?
I really think you need to try
and stay out of Ebina's business.
You listening to me?
I'm listening.
But we're not really getting into Ebina's business.
You are.
It's obvious.
And it's starting to get really annoying.
Annoying, huh?
You should know there's someone
else who's wanting us to do this.
Anyway it's not like you're the
one who is directly affected by it.
What?
Huh?
But I will be affected by this.
Listen... If you're going out with Yui,
then you've gotten to know Ebina, right?
I-I-I'm not going out with her, I
don't know why you're saying that.
You're totally misunderstanding me. So gross.
No way Yui would go out with you.
That's not what I mean.
I mean that you must know how things
are because you're hanging out with Yui.
Gross.
Seriously, you don't have to say it like that again.
There are a lot of guys who say
Ebina's a catch if she would just shut up.
So they ask me to introduce them.
But when I try to do that, she always sweetly declines.
I thought she was shy at first...
I was pretty persistent with introducing her...
But the more I tried she would say...
"Hey... enough already, okay?"
She said that to me, like I was someone else.
It was odd.
Ebina doesn't really talk
about herself... and I don't pry.
But I'm sure she hates this type of thing.
But that's a bit wrong.
If you have to sacrifice part of
yourself in order to protect something,
you'd probably give up and throw it all away.
Even the relationships you have now.
So listen... we're having a good time. So...
Could you just mind your own business?
If that's it, don't worry...
Hm?
Hayama said not to be concerned about it, okay?
What do you mean?
If Hayato says so then I guess we're fine.
Wow, awesome!
We're gonna take a break, aren't we?
What a great view! You can see the whole city from here!
Yes, we are.
Oh, it's Tobecchi!
Huh?
Yahallo!
Isn't it amazing up here? You can see the whole city...
You haven't forgotten what we
talked about, right, Hikitani?
Hm... I haven't.
So, how's it going with the guy relationships?
Intimate yet?
We're getting along fine, I guess.
At night we play cards and stuff.
Well, if I can't see it, I can't actually enjoy it!
Honestly Hikitani it would be best
if you could do a bit more to
gather all the boys in a place
where I can enjoy the view, as well!
Well... it looks like we're going
to Arashiyama, so we could do it then.
That'd be perfect!
You're going to spoil your dinner that way.
Then I'll just give the rest to Hikki.
I don't want to eat that.
Why are you taking a weird little bite out of each item?
I would more likely eat it if it were bit in half.
What should I do with all this, Yukinon?
I'll help eat some of it.
Don't just stand there, eat.
I guess I can help eat some too.
'Kay.
Here.
It's like you're trying to feed an animal.
It's not bad. Food you don't have
to work for is more delicious, anyway.
Wow!
This place is so amazing!
It really is.
Look at the ground.
Oh look a lantern?
It should be here!
This place is perfect!
Whaddya mean?
I... mean for a confession... that is.
Why the passive voice?
You're right, I think this is a perfect location.
Yeah... that's great!
For a win-or-lose match... here is good.
Oh man, I'm nervous.
Oh god!
You're gonna be okay.
And you'll be getting a real girlfriend.
You might even stop hanging out with me, man.
No way, don't even say that!
Oh man, I'm really nervous though!
Wow, even I'm getting a little bit nervous now.
Hey, Tobe.
Huh? Oh no is something the matter?
I think I'm going crazy over here, Hayato!
Well then, just forgot about it.
What the heck!
I thought I'd come and tell you good luck,
but then I looked at your face and lost courage.
That's so rude!
But it actually helped me relax, somehow.
You're being awfully uncooperative.
Am I really?
Yes, you are.
It kind of feels like you're
getting in the way on purpose.
I didn't really mean to.
But I like how everything is now.
I like Tobe and Hina,
and the time we all spend together, that's why.
If you can be broken by something like
this, you weren't really friends to begin with.
You might be right...
But...
The things you lose will never come back.
It's really weird to think that such a
shallow relationship could possibly work out.
Maybe so.
But I don't think of any of my friends as being shallow.
For now my environment... really means everything to me.
Nope, they are shallow.
So, what happens to Tobe?
I told him so many times to give up.
I don't think Hina's going to open her heart to him.
But you don't know what will happen in the future.
I just didn't want Tobe to move so quickly on this yet.
How selfish.
These are just your own circumstances.
Maybe.
Well tell me about you, then?
What would you do here?
It doesn't matter what I'd do in this situation.
If it were up to me, thinking about it would be useless.
Hayama and I are different.
As well as, Tobe.
It really doesn't matter what I'd do,
it has zero bearing on this situation
and would be completely useless.
So basically, you don't want
anything to change around here, correct?
Yeah. That's right.
You know, you're the last person
I wanted to ask for help here...
Believe me, same here, moron.
I don't know what Hayama is trying to protect.
And quite honestly... it's okay if I don't know...
Because there are things I can do.
Tobe.
H-Hikitani...
Seriously, man...
I'm really freakin' nervous here.
So, what will you do if you get rejected tonight?
Isn't it mean to ask right before I do this?
It's fine, hurry up and answer. Ebina is on her way.
I'm won't give up on pursuing her.
You know me I don't usually care about this kind of stuff.
But this time I really mean it, I'm super serious!
Really?
Then you must make sure to give
it your all until the very end.
Yeah!
You're an okay guy after all, Hikitani!
No, I'm not! Idiot!
See you do have some good points.
So, what brought all that about?
Let's not get too excited just yet.
Tobe's gonna get rejected.
Well that's a possibility.
I guess... maybe.
But there might be a way things can work out for the best.
And what's that entail?
That's fine, we'll leave it all up to you then.
Yeah.
Huh?
So, um...
Hm?
First of all, Tobe is absolutely going to get rejected.
Tobe has some realization of what could happen...
but the others...
Tobe isn't the only one who thinks
their relationship is important.
That's why she made her request of me.
And that's why he was agonizing over it.
"I don't wanna lose this."
"I wanna hold on to that hand."
The three of them have the same wish.
I, um...
Uh...
I...
So in order to keep Tobe from getting rejected...
to keep the group together...
and to stay friends with Ebina...
there's really only one thing I can do...
and that is...
Um... Well, uh...
I...
Uh...
I, uh...
I've really liked you for a long time!
Please go out with me!
I'm sorry.
I don't want to go out with anyone right now.
No matter who were to ask me out, I wouldn't date them.
Huh...
If that's all you want, I'm going.
Uh...
There you go.
Hikitani... that wasn't right.
I mean it's good I knew before I got rejected,
but still, man... that wasn't right.
It just means now's not the right time.
We can still enjoy the relationships we have right now.
Yeah, I guess, that's true.
I mean she can't feel this way forever.
Hikitani...
Sorry, dude... but I won't let you win her!
Man... I thought I was gonna have a heart attack!
Sorry.
I knew that was the only way
you knew how to do it, but still...
I'm sorry.
I don't need your apologies.
I hate the way you choose to do things.
Yukinon...
I don't know why... I can't really explain it,
But the way you handle things... I hate it.
Yukinon...
I'm going back.
Uh, I guess we should go back too.
Sure.
So uh, that plan wasn't so good, huh?
I know we were all a bit shocked, and
Hina's timing for everything was slightly off...
Yeah.
But... wow, it was still surprising.
I thought you were serious for a moment.
Nope, I wasn't.
I know, right?
But...
But really...
Don't do these things... not anymore.
That was the most effective way I knew how.
That's all it was.
It doesn't always have to be about being effective.
But some people didn't want a resolution.
And some wanted to keep things how they were.
You can't meet everyone's needs.
While I said that, I realized
something. This didn't make sense.
It was the deception I hated most in the world.
Tobecchi didn't get rejected...
the boys seem to be getting along nicely...
and Hina is totally fine with everything...
So now we can all just get back to normal again...
like nothing has changed at all.
But...
You need to be more...
considerate... of people's feelings!
How do you know so much about
everything, but still not understand that?
I really don't like it... not at all.
Hello hello!
Did I keep you waiting?
No.
I thought I should come thank you.
You don't really have to.
We didn't really solve what we talked about.
On the surface, yes.
But... you knew what I meant.
When she said she wanted the boys to get along...
she meant she wanted to keep them at a distance.
She also wanted us to try and
prevent Tobe from asking her out.
She probably talked to Hayama about it, too..
And that's why he was so troubled the whole
time and only tried to do things half-way.
Thanks for what you did.
You really helped me out.
Tobe may seem like a garbage person,
but I actually think he's a pretty decent guy.
No, I know that.
But if I were to date someone right now, it
just wouldn't go well... you know what I mean?
I don't believe-
It wouldn't.
I'm just... a rotten fujoshi.
Well, then... it is what it is.
Yeah.
It is what it is.
You know... maybe it would go
well if I went out with you instead.
Don't joke like that.
Uh...
You know if you go and say things like
that to me, I might end up falling for you.
You almost had me there...
I like how you're open with people
who don't matter... at least to you.
That's funny.
I actually really like that part of my personality, too.
Sounds like we have that in common since I also like
how I can say things that I don't actually really mean.
I'm good with me...
and I'm happy with how things
are going at this particular moment.
It's been a long time since I've had something like this,
so I don't want to lose it.
I like where I am, and the people who are with me.
That's why...
Sometimes I hate myself for it.
Everyone, has something that's important to them,
and they don't want to lose it.
So they hide... and they pretend.
That's why they tell lies.
But...
The biggest liar of all...
is me.
It's quiet without big bro around.
Right, Kaa?
I wonder if things are going okay for him.
It's boring without him around.
Let's play, Kaa!
Good kitty! You're so cute!
So soft and silky! Good kitty! Good kitty!
Whoa, where are you going, Kaa?
I hope he'll come back soon.