What are you guys gonna do?
Hina and I are taking liberal arts,
and Yumiko is still thinking about it.
Oh really? Maybe I'll go towards liberal arts, too...
What about you?
I'm pretty sure I've decided I
just need to think on it more.
Oooohh...
Hey, Hayato, which path is better?
It's YOUR future, so you better
take it seriously or you may regret it.
That's true.
By the way, Hayato.
Is it true that you're going out with Yukinoshita?
What?!
Who thought that was a good thing to say?
Sorry. I just heard a rumor.
Hey, so did you hear about Hayama?
There were some girls that saw
them together during winter break.
Yeah... seems true, right?
Over here, Yukinon!
Why do we have to move...
Happy Birthday!
Th-thank you.
So Yukinoshita, your birthday
is actually on January 3rd, right?
And my birthday is April 16th in case you're wondering.
I didn't ask. By the way, why
are you even in here right now?
Oh come on... it's fine, isn't it, guys?
Actually, I've kinda got a
little favor to ask of all of you.
Uh, so um...
I heard a little rumor earlier, are
you and Hayama going out, Yukinoshita?
What?
So, Isshiki...
Y-Yes?
You know that there's no way that's true, right?
Oh, right, of course!
I totally knew that rumor was
a big lie, no way it was true!
Must be when we all met up the other day
I guess someone saw that and got the wrong idea.
Ah, I see... some low-life with ulterior motives...
But don't they say gossip usually only lasts 49 days?
75 days actually.
Which is fine if that were the case...
It's kind of strange but Hayama hasn't had any
real rumors linking him to anyone up until now.
It felt more like he belonged to everyone.
But now it seems like, since this rumor,
there are more and more girls coming out of the
woodwork trying to get him, they're always around him.
What does that mean?
Well, like directly asking him out...
Even if they don't go that far, they still
try to flirt with him in some way or other.
Seriously I don't understand what you even mean?
How do you flirt with someone like that?
Um, hey there...
So are you dating anyone special...
at the moment?
Not really... I'm not.
You see that? They're all
coming up to Hayama just like that!
But that was because of the way you said it. Right, Hikki?
Well, uh... most guys wouldn't find that unappealing.
I mean, it really struck a chord in me.
Hikki?
Why are you so quiet all of a sudden?
Uh... W-Well.. I mean...
I get Hayama's situation. Yes, I actually do get it.
Ah! Those look great on you, Yukinon!
Oh, you think so?
Yeah... they do.
Thanks, I guess.
Have you always worn glasses?
They're blue-light blocking glasses.
Really? Maybe I should try some
of those, too, what do you think?
You don't even really use computers, do you?
That's not fair I do use them. I use them a lot!
Yukinon, will you let me see them for a minute?
Oh, we got a message.
Do you have minute?
I've got something I wanna talk about...
Uh...
Okay, I'm counting on you for the
career plan consultation meeting!
What? I thought you wanted to talk?
See ya later!
What did you want to talk about?
What exactly is going on with you and Hayato?
Actually there's nothing going on at all.
I have just known him for quite a long time.
Really?
Tell me, Miura, is there anything I gain by lying to you?
Seriously... girls like you are always on me.
What? Why are you talking to me with that kind of tone?
Hey. You're really pissing me off. I hate...
Yumiko!
I promise we just ran into him randomly!
I've already explained it to you.
That's ALL it was.
But if it really was only that...
He wouldn't have cared so much.
There's just gotta be more to it.
And I'm not talking about right now...
What about in the past?
Even if there'd been something,
and I told you about it in detail,
what do you think it'd change for you?
Would you or anyone else, even believe it?
In the end, it's meaningless.
I really hate that-
Is there anything else you'd like to say to me?
Hey, you should try to calm down a bit... kay?
You need to calm down as well.
Don't worry I'm calm.
I'm used to it. This always happens.
As long as the people I am close to understand,
then nothing else really matters.
Well, of course. That's exactly why...
I want to be close like that to Hayama.
I want to be just like that.
That's why I want to know.
What happened between them before,
you're not really interested
in knowing about that, are you?
I just... Well, I... I thought...
I just thought... it would be really nice if we
could be together for just a little bit longer...
And... I just don't want it to be like this.
Hayato's... been acting pretty distant lately...
I know that it's kinda weird for me.
I'm just... at a loss and don't know what else to do.
It isn't weird.
Honestly, it isn't weird at all.
Wanting to stay together is normal.
Don't ever feel bad for wanting that.
Miura wants to know Hayato's future plans,
and wants to know what exactly
he plans on doing with his life.
Surely she know that things can't always stay
the way they are or how she wants them to stay.
Nevertheless, she wishes to stay by his side.
But you know, Miura,
Have you thought about why he hasn't told you?
Maybe it means he doesn't want you to know.
Maybe he'll hate you for prying.
Hey, Hikki enough!
Hikigaya...
With that said, you still wanna know?
I do.
Even with that chance. It's all I've got for now.
I understand. I'll figure something out.
Here, for you.
Oh, thank you.
So, you're using it right away, huh.
It's okay if you guys go home.
Hikki.. We can't just leave everything up to you.
It's fine. It's probably easier to ask him alone. So...
Well.. We're sorry to leave it all up to you though.
No worries. That's how the job is sometimes.
That line doesn't suit you.
My career plans?
Does someone want to know about that?
No, just asking... ya know for reference.
Hmm... Well, can I ask you a favor as well, then?
You can be quite annoying. Can you stop doing that?
Come on, man. What would you do if I said that to you?
It'd be weird, right?
I'll think about that type of thing when it happens.
I see...
My answer?
I will leave to your imagination.
Career plans, huh?
I guess since I've worked so hard playing tennis,
I would probably do something that relates.
Couldn't you get recruited or something like that?
That happens only to a lucky few.
There's no one really here to
be recruited except maybe Hayama.
Everyone, break!
See you guys after school!
Doesn't suit me, huh?
Oh, no I...
Just surprised to see you be so
leader-like. I haven't seen it...
I didn't expect it I guess.
I'm doing a pretty good job aren't I?
Even if I'm maybe a bit undependable.
No, you're dependable.
I guess I don't really know yet, but...
Uh.. I mean...
You... probably are.
Oh! You're late... Come on.
Oh! And thanks so much to the both of you as well!
Yahallo, Iroha!
What would you like for us to do?
We really need to get this room rearranged.
And the alumni are coming by as well.
The Alumni are coming?
Well, if it isn't Hikigaya!
Yahallo!
Hey, Sis... I have a question for you.
Hayato's career plans? Why such an interest?
Do you know anything about them?
Just when I thought you'd started doing things yourself...
you're asking people for favors just like in the past...
However back then when you were
really little, it was super cute...
Just go figure and it out for yourself.
Yukinon...
Will you walk me to the station!
What?
I can imagine it's not often you get to walk
home with such a beautiful young lady such as myself.
Kay! Shall we go?
Ahhh. Whatever...
Did you ask Yukino what major she was going to pursue?
No... I didn't.
Well, I guess she won't say it herself.
But seriously, you'd better ask her, Hikigaya.
We'll check our answers next time.
Technically I don't think we can
really call her response an answer.
Don't worry about the details, silly!
Speaking of... did you ask Hayato directly?
Yeah. He had a lot to say,
but none of it answered the question at all.
Oh, is that so? So Hayato expected it, too?
Why's that?
For someone to help find him... maybe?
"Everyone's Hayama Hayato".
I'm not as good of a guy... as you think I am.
Hello?
Hey... it's me. I'm sorry. I know it's little late.
It's okay, what's up?
I need a favor.
You've got this, Hayama!
Good luck on going for yet another win this year!
H-Hayato... G-Good luck out there!
While I'm at it, good luck to you, too!
Thanks!
No, no.. Not you, Tobe!
Do your best! Okay.
I wish you luck.
Alright... let's do this.
On your mark! Get set!
I'm so glad I rode my bike to school today.
There's no way I'd be able to do this otherwise.
You're really keeping up with me.
Well, yeah. If I don't think about pacing myself,
it's not impossible.
I wonder what people think when they get close
to the point of no return on a difficult task?
If there's still half left, does it feel hopeless?
Or is there a sense of relief
since they've already come halfway?
I imagine people feel either one way or the other.
And both of those feelings, no matter what,
make a gap in people's hearts.
That's why... I've pushed myself this far.
Was Miura just a convenient
way to try and avoid other girls?
How about it? Did you find her useful?
Will you just shut up?
Which did you choose, humanities or science?
Fine, I'll put it this way.
Pick the sciences.
I have no idea what you picked. And I don't really care.
But there's still time to change it, so pick the sciences.
Don't you understand that's going to
be the only way to get what you want?
What I want?
Didn't you tell me to quit
doing these annoying things to you?
I get it. All you want is to be freed
from everyone's great expectations of you.
Not many people pick the sciences. Even less girls do,
they all seem like they wanna go the liberal arts route.
You can start to distance yourself
from the things holding you back
if you choose a different path from everyone else.
Besides, if you do decide to take a different path...
then people will understand that and move on.
If your group simply moves
on... no one will ever get hurt.
And the best part, you won't have betrayed anyone.
I knew it... we could never have been friends.
I really hate your guts you know that?
Okay.
I feel like I'm inferior to you, and I can't stand that.
I want us to be equals.
That way, I can actually accept losing to you.
Therefore, that's why I'm not going to do as you suggest.
Sorry I've ruined your chances of winning again.
You didn't. I'll win. Cause that's just who I am.
Moreover, I don't want to lose to the likes of you.
Dammit... Aren't you the cool one?
Congratulations on your win, Hayama!
I just knew going in that you'd win this race, any words?
Thanks to everyone's support today, I was
able to push through and make it to the end.
My thanks to you.
Yumiko...
Iroha...
thanks, everyone.
Let's hear a round of applause for Hayama!
No one cares about the losers, right?
Well I'm guessing he wasn't dating Yukinoshita after all.
Yeah, looks like there wasn't any truth to the rumors.
Hey, Hikigaya?
What happened to you?
I was taking a break and they
got worried and sent me here.
Oh... did you get hurt?
Yeah... a little.
I wonder why they didn't take
care of that for you over there?
No one was there when I reached the finish line.
So I see you have bad timing.
Or is it your luck that's so bad? Or maybe bad eyes?
I guess it could be...
My personality, my attitude, take your pick.
Looks like you can't keep your hands to yourself.
Go have a seat over there.
No... I can take care of this on my own thank you.
Just sit down.
Ow... uh... that really stings.
Of course it does. I'm disinfecting it.
It's only natural that it'd be effective on you.
Please... you don't need to talk to
me like I'm some sort of gross germ.
Well did you figure anything out while running?
Hayama say anything?
Yeah.
He's definitely not choosing science... so.
That's an odd way to put it.
All done.
Uh... Th-Thanks... for doing this.
It's not... a big deal seriously okay?
Hey.
Can I... ask you which major you're thinking about?
That is the first time you've
ever asked me something like that.
Uh, really?
For the time being I'm going with liberal arts.
So... which means.. We'll be in it together.
Well, we'll be in the same field, at the very least.
Kay... I'm gonna head back to the classroom.
Kay.
I'll... See you.
Whoa... Oh hey there!
Oh, Hikki...
Hey, Yuigahama.
Oh.. Yeah. I seriously just got here.
Hey Yukinon, I'm sorry I'm so late. So...
Yumiko and everyone are going to celebrate.
Will you come?
I'm sorry. About those weird rumors...
I'm sure they caused you trouble.
I wouldn't say it was that bad.
Also... I'm just really grateful that
you were actually looking out for me.
Yukino... you've really changed a bit.
Have I?
It's just... things around here
are a lot different than back then.
Yukinon!
The food came! There's so much chicken!
And it's roasted! C'mon!
You know she really has changed over time.
Seems she's not chasing after Haruno anymore.
But... maybe that's just it though huh?
Well that's a good thing, isn't it?
You haven't noticed it?
Noticed?
Well... If you don't get it, I guess its no big deal.
Oh, yeah. I forgot to tell you something.
Relationships don't always end...
simply because you go off to college.
No... they're always changing.
That's just you, Hikigaya. I'm not really like you.
Oh yeah, then why didn't you tell
anyone about your decision, then?
When you pick from the only
option that you have to choose from,
you can't really call that your own decision, now can you?
I forgot to tell you something.
So I... really hate your guts, too.
Wow, do you really?
That's the first time anyone has said that to me
right to my face.
Even so... I refuse to choose... anything.
I truly think that's the best
way to deal with things, you know.
That's just being selfish.
Oh. So Hayato's chosen liberal arts.
Then... maybe I'll go with that, too.
Is it really that simple of a choice?
I mean, there's not really anything I want to do.
I can take time off for the exams,
but I can't really do that with this.
I'd hate to be your boyfriend.
What? I don't want to hear that from you, Hikio.
It's just, well...
like, even if I include all the annoying things,
I guess it's fine, after all...
Oh... So its fine to have simple reasons...