Huh?
Komachi!
What?
Uh...
Can I get you coffee?
Yeah.
Okay.
Here you go.
Hold up... Komachi.
Can I talk to you?
Okay, I'll listen.
However, don't you have something to say to me?
Uh...
Sorry about earlier.
I shouldn't have said what I said to you.
It wasn't just what you said to me.
Your attitude and your personality were bad, as well.
Your eyes too.
That's true.
At any rate, I'm sure there's
something else you did that was bad.
Also, true.
And you didn't apologize.
Ah, you're right.
But since it's you, Big Brother, it's okay.
And since I'm your little sister.
I'll forgive you.
Also... I'm really sorry for my behavior.
What, don't worry about that.
I forgive you. Because I'm your big bro.
You really can be quite full of yourself, can't you Bro?
So you gonna tell me what happened?
It's a long story.
That's okay.
I swear... that's just like you.
I mean, I do understand where you're
coming from because I'm your sister...
And we've lived together for
basically forever, so I get it.
I can say "wow, you are so dumb" then smile and move on.
While thinking "He can't be helped" and that's it.
Truthfully... I get a bit sad.
But it's different for other people.
They don't understand what you're
thinking and it can be hard on them.
You're nice to me and treat me as an equal...
but I think you're only capable of
that because I'm your little sister.
And most likely, if I weren't your sister...
you wouldn't talk to me or even come anywhere near me.
Well, aside from that point,
I'm really lucky to have you as my sister, you know.
I bet I got a lot of points from that line.
Uh! Wow Big Brother that's so...
That's sweet but if you weren't my big brother,
I absolutely wouldn't come near you and
would completely ignore you so there's that.
Maybe so but I do have some good
points, wouldn't you agree Little Sister?
Nope not at all. You're actually really annoying.
Hm...
But you know...
If you are together with someone for 15 long
years, you can't really help but grow attached to them.
Oh, I bet you I got a lot of points from that great line!
Well, 15 years is a long time.
And then another fifteen.
Actually, more time will pass because
we have all the time in the world.
Quit yammering.
How many years do you think I've
been listening to you yammer on and on?
And will keep listening for many more to come!
Do you get it?
Y-yeah...
It's not only you.
I have a future I need to protect too.
I really like Yukino and Yui a lot, they're super cool.
So if you break up the club, I'm going to be upset.
So please... just for my sake...
and for the sakes of my friends... can't you do something?
Well if it's for you, I guess I'll have to.
Mhm. Doing it for me is a great idea.
But that's just because I'm so selfish...
I really can't help it.
That is so true.
Thanks for the talk.
You're welcome Big Brother.
After all that...
that's the answer Komachi gave me.
I was searching for the reason somewhere...
to protect that place... and the time we all spend there.
To prevent Yukino Yukinoshita and Yui
Yuigahama from becoming student council president,
what can Hachiman Hikigaya do?
Well,
I have no idea and that sucks!!
I know, how about getting rid of our uniforms?
That's great!
It would also be good if there were no more bag checks.
Those are really annoying.
They always seem to find the sexy
manga I've borrowed from my friends...
That's just you...
I'll write it down.
Please do not write that down.
More important than "no more checking
our bags," I want to eat lunch on the roof.
Oh, that's a great idea!
Ugh!
Oh, so pitiful, Hachiman Hikigaya!
Stop saying dumb things.
This pitifulness is my default.
Something you want?
Foolish question!
I'm always hunkered down here during the lunch hour.
Anyways my eyes came upon your
sadness, so I came to give you attention.
What's wrong with you?
Don't worry it's really not all that important.
Wanna talk about it?
No, that's okay.
Nothing anyone else needs to care or worry about.
Don't be an idiot.
Tell me Hachiman, to what extent have you
painfully listened to my drivel over the years?
I'll listen to your idle gossip, since it's you.
You know I'll admit I think I'm pretty cool here...
lending a hand to the weak.
Only what you said before that last thing was cool.
So... did you steal that line?
Nope... they're all my gems.
Idiot.
You know you're not really saying anything cool right now.
Zaimokuza, I have a favor to ask.
Uh... um..
So, now as for how we can go about doing this...
Oh! There you are.
Whoa!
Hey, what are you doing here?
Since you're out here working really hard for me Bro...
I thought I should be doing the same for you!
Ta-da!
I found people who'll gladly work with you Bro!
I can't believe I'm helping out.
And do it with a smile.
Let's start the "Campaign to Retain Yukino and Yui"!
Oh yeah!
Not that I really care...
But if Yukinoshita and Yuigahama don't end up
running, who's going to be president in the end?
Uh...
Come on now...
Um... tell me why we have to prevent
those two from being elected again?
Really... I'm thinking going to war with
those two could be a very big mistake on our part.
Yes, that is very true but...
Big Brother I wanna keep the service club
operating and I must have Yukino and Yui in it.
Honestly I don't care about the student council elections.
Okay?
Then what do I do about Isshiki?
Well whoever this Isshiki person
may be, is she important to you?
No, not at all.
Then, why are you worried about it?
Because a request is still a request Komachi.
So, what's more important to you, your job or me?
That's dumb, you, of course.
I've no desire to work.
Process of elimination.
Well I guess I don't have to be happy about it...
But, okay.
So what are you going to do about it?
Let's see.
The thing I should give the utmost
priority to is Komachi's request:
Keeping Yukinoshita and Yuigahama in the club.
Supporting the other candidates
is a difficult situation...
so the card left to me is...
I can go try negotiating with Isshiki.
Not gonna happen, she's a girl.
Will she even understand you?
If Iroha Isshiki is playing that particular character...
I'm going to say I'll have an easy negotiation.
In the end... Isshiki just
wants to protect her brand image.
So because of that...
she wants to avoid the high risk-low
return issue of a vote of no confidence.
Which means...
My first approach was a mistake.
Kawasaki.
Hm?
Who do you think would be a
good student council president?
Can you come up with a list of names?
Huh?
I'm thinking you too, I guess?
Ha, that's really funny.
There's no way I'd be able to
get nominations from 30 people.
I know that. I just wanted to say it.
Big Bro...
Talk to Yukino and Yui about this, okay?
Promise me?
Yeah, but when I go present the idea
to them, I need to sound persuasive.
So first I need to prepare.
I'm worried that bad things will happen since
you're the type to argue for the sake of arguing.
It'll be okay.
I've now got a reason, a
problem, and a solution established.
I just need to put it into action.
Oh, I would like you to put LCD tablets in the art room.
LCD tablets?
One-third of the whole student body, huh?
It is I.
We've got enough numbers... I'm
going to move on to the next step now.
Uh... This is not really a good tactic.
This is fraught with danger.
Zaimokuza...
Oh, don't misunderstand me.
It is not you I'm worried about!
You see, I also assume responsibility by assisting,
and the anxiety that you will
blame me for everything is terrible.
And believe me in that instance, I am
prepared to tell everyone everything!
You really are such trash Zaimokuza. Never change.
It's okay though.
They can search all they want.
The person behind these accounts doesn't exist.
No one's going to get hurt.
Just keep this in mind...
As long as you don't go and make a
problem a problem, it won't be seen as one.
Can you get Isshiki for me?
Ah!
Oh...
Sorry, it's only me.
Copying down all of this stuff
is really difficult you know!
Oh, so by the way, was the girl you were
hanging out with the other day Hayama's girlfriend?
I have no idea.
Come on, surely it's okay if you tell me... isn't it?
When this is over.
Whatever I don't really think that
will be much of a problem for me.
Don't you think so too?
So anyway... speaking of him do you like...
what do you think about him?
Huh?
Are you trying to hit on me right now?
Sorry, it can't happen, I have a crush on someone else.
No, that's not it.
I was just simply asking you
what you thought about Hayama.
Oh...
Hm... let me think about it for a second.
At first I thought he was so cute, and I wanted to ki...
I wanted to hold hands with him, or something but...
You just almost said you wanted to "kiss" him?
So anyways...
Is there really a point in doing all of this?
It's not like there isn't one.
You know the way you said that just now was kinda vague...
There's no way to win against Yukinoshita
or Yuigahama... no matter what you do.
It's pointless in that way.
Well, not that I would really want to...
but I think it would be super
scary if I actually won the election.
It's not like you're gonna really win this.
Yeah... well...
Besides, whoever those people who nominated you
were, they won't really vote for you, will they?
Those people are probably laughing hard right now.
And, when they see you lose the
election, they'll laugh even more about it.
That would make you mad, wouldn't it?
However... wouldn't you want to give
them a taste of their own medicine?
I do... well... I could do it I know I can...
You can.
You've been writing for quite a while now.
Do you know what that is?
It's the list of nominators, right?
That's right. However...
This here is the list of people that nominated you.
Uh...
Huh?
But I already have enough, how can I possible
have more than the amount required to run?
The rule says that there must be
at least thirty people to run...
but it's okay if you gather more.
Someone is running an Isshiki support account, online.
If just one-third of the student body supports you...
then you can easily go and win this election.
I don't get where this came from? That's not possible.
And even if I were to win this
thing, I wouldn't be a good president.
I don't have confidence in myself.
Plus I already belong to a club.
I agree it would be difficult to deal with both.
But what you would gain would be huge.
What do you think it is?
What?
Well, experience or something like that.
And maybe a good recommendation.
So for the record here... you're acting like a teacher.
That's wrong.
The thing you gain is the chance to say...
"Even though I'm a freshman and student council
president, I'm doing my best and showing up to practice!"
See?
Ew.
And when you're a freshman,
and you mess up, you're forgiven.
You also have the excuse of going to
practice when student council gets annoying.
And the opposite is also true.
Yea, but it's still gonna be really difficult for me.
What do I do?
When those times happen, you can consult Hayama.
Huh?
It's okay to accept his help.
Hey, maybe you can make him keep an eye out for
you and walk you home after practice sometimes.
No way, how are you actually even this smart?
I just am.
Hm...
If this many people are supporting
me, I guess I can't say no.
You know I've gotta say... your
suggestion is quite attractive.
Let me tell you...
it really hurts me being laughed
at by the kids in my class.
Okay, I'll work with you. Let's win this!
Have you changed your minds yet?
No I haven't. This is the best strategy.
Mine hasn't changed, either.
It's not necessary for you to run, too.
It is. And I don't wanna lose.
Actually why are you running?
Because, if you aren't here Yukinon, the club will end.
I don't want that to happen.
It's not going to come to that.
It will!
The truth is, you don't have to run in the election.
Not just you, Yuigahama, you too, Yukinoshita.
What are you even talking about?
I'm pretty sure we rejected your crazy plan.
You did, but it's not that plan.
Huh?
I already gave up on that.
Did you have something to do with this?
An interested party...
I don't really know who it was though.
I see.
An amazing number of people.
Yeah, it's about about one-third of
the student body of the high school.
This number is the actual truth.
Although, it was impossible to
gather this much support for Isshiki...
In other words, there's just one big lie in the moon.
I got it, okay?
Later man.
Out!
This is nothing but junk.
It was just a tool used to persuade them.
So... I just need to get through this day,
and then get rid of the support accounts.
Erase all of it.
In order for Isshiki to be president...
I cleared all the requirements
and the shackles holding her down.
So, there's no need for you to run
for student council president anymore.
So a support account, huh?
Well I'm glad.
So, this is settled, right?
So... I see...
You're telling us there's no
reason we need to act anymore.
Yeah, I guess you don't, huh.
Yes.
I really thought you of all people would understand.
Uh?
Huh?
I guess I'll go tell the teachers.
Uh! We'll come.
Just one of us is enough.
Um... Sorry about that.
Huh? Why are you apologizing?
Well, you really worked on this didn't you?
Like, your public pledge, and the speech, and stuff.
Oh that... that doesn't really matter.
I bet you did a lot too, didn't you, Hikki?
Oh wow, your hair has grown all long and straggly.
Here, let me fix it.
It doesn't need fixing.
There, there.
I bet you did your best too, huh?
Not really...
This place is important to me.
And you somehow protected it.
Hey...
I knew that I probably wouldn't
beat Yukinon for the presidency,
but then I also worried that if I did win, then I
wouldn't be able to come to the club activities anymore.
And I have you to thank for all of this.
You're wrong about that.
That's enough.
You did your best, Hikki!
What are you saying?
Hikki did his best, huh?
Stop... I didn't really do anything.
That's true.
I mean nothing we can actually see, right?
But then again I know you...
I bet you did something you didn't want to do.
Maybe you wanted to change your ways...
however it's not something you can easily do.
And your guilty conscious lingers.
I couldn't really do anything,
but even so I wondered if this was the right thing to do.
So, it will probably bother you more, Hikki.
Now we can go back to how it was before.
I don't know about that.
I really thought you of all people would understand.
This club is not really that difficult to deal with,
and I understand how the
student council activities work...
There are people that can't act...
if they are not given a problem...
and they can't find a reason.
The only thing that remained for me...
was the suspicion, I had made a big mistake.
Do you start working today?
I sure do!
You know, I kinda don't think it'll
go so well in the beginning, though.
Next year my little sister will enter this school.
Oh?
Listen, you better try and do a good job.
Ah!
What? Are you trying to hit on me? You are
being too obvious! It's uncomfortable! Sorry!
Seems you had a different reason for rejecting me before.
Good luck to you then...
Oh, Hikigaya.
I can grab that.
Thanks! I had more things than I thought.
Ugh!
Seems like it's a different room, huh?
Man, I was really gunning for her too.
What?
I had thought Yukinoshita would
become the student council president.
And then Yuigahama would become the vice president.
And you'd be general affairs!
You gave me a minor position? Wow.
And, when I've graduated, I would sometimes come back...
just to hang with you guys during meetings...
And then I'd get to say things like,
"The cultural festival and the
sports festival were so much fun!"
And you guys did that!
You know... I've always dreamt of that.
I've been thinking about consequences.
What if... And this is purely hypothetical...
What if we could go back to the last
save point and make a different choice?
What do you think would've happened?
Would things have been different?
The answer is no.
Okay, surely that's everything by now, right, Iroha?
Tobe, the refrigerator needs to
move, it's supposed to go in the corner.
And the heater goes next to the desk.
Aww... You should've told me that before.
Hey, Iroha, I've gotta head
out to my seasonal Christmas job!
But I'm bored now, and I want to finish remodeling
the student council room as soon as possible.
O-okay.
But I need to get to work.
I wish Hayato would hurry up and get here!
Uh. Hayama?
Okay, Tobe! You can go ahead and leave right now.
O-okay.