Komachi's Present List:
Bookstore gift card. Gift card.
Major household appliances.
But.. The thing I want the most is your eternal happiness!
Eek! I seriously got a whole lot of points for that one!
Oh and also... We're out of detergent,
so pick some up on your way home.
Idiot.
Oh, hey big brother... welcome home!
You shouldn't study at the heated table.
You could end up falling asleep
under it and then catch a nasty cold.
These tables aren't all that good for people.
You say as you make yourself
comfortable at one of those tables.
By the way, Komachi...
What is this here?
Oh that? It's just what it looks like.
Oh?
This girl really wants major household appliances?
She's my sister, but what in the world...
Thank you big brother.
Oh yeah! I almost forgot, Mom
wants you to order the chicken.
Chicken?
And cake, too.
Oh, that too, huh?
I told her I'd do it, but she didn't
listen. Even though I've done it every year.
It's done out of parental love.
She just wants you to focus on your entrance exams.
Stop it.. You're putting a lot of pressure on me.
Sorry. I couldn't come up with anything else to say.
This is difficult.
I guess hearing that from a slacker would piss anyone off.
So you know... at times like these, "I love you" is good.
Is that so?
Well then, I love you, little sis.
Well, I don't necessarily feel
the same, but I appreciate it!
You're so rude...
Hikki... Are you going to the club today?
I know, I know. I'm going.
Yeah, so we better get moving.
I'm gonna get my bag!
Tell me why you're going ahead of me again?
I'm standing here waiting for you, aren't I?
Uh so.. I'll probably leave early today.
I mean.. I might have to leave early for a little while.
You're going to help Iroha, huh?
So you know then.
Well it's easy to tell if you just pay attention!
Yukinoshita as well?
I'm not sure if she does or not.
She doesn't ever really talk about you.
So then.. You're doing it alone?
I am.. But really I'm just doing it
because I guess I sort of owe it to her.
You don't have to worry about it.
I am worried.
You have more important things
to concern yourself with than me.
I wonder if Yukinon wanted to
be student council president.
Don't know.
Well either way.. We really should've
accepted that request together as a club.
I Kina feel that.. Old Yukinon
would've liked the challenge.
So why do you think that's the case?
Because...
I believe Yukinon is the type of person who'd
want a chance to try to overcome that sort of thing.
So.. I kinda thought that would've
been a really good start, but...
You think so?
Sure.. In the past she probably would've.
But I'm not really sure about now.
Yeah...
Yahallo!
Oh hi, glad you're here.
Hey.
Um...
You got a moment?
Sure, what is it?
You okay if I leave early for a while?
Well let's see..
It's not like we are especially
busy at the moment right now.
Well, uh, yeah you're right...
I have a lot I need to... do.
Komachi's cramming for exams...
Oh that's right.
Yea, it's probably better like this, huh?
There's not really anything we as a club
can give to Komachi to help her with those.
I think we should let Hikki do as much as he can!
Okay, Yukinon?
Sure.. Let's do that.
Thanks you guys.
Great then!
I'm going to shoot a text over to Komachi.
Where's Isshiki?
I haven't seen her yet.
Weren't you with her?
Have you heard anything?
I was texting her earlier about the meeting...
but no response. Maybe she's still over at practice.
Gotta say it louder! Huh?
She said she had something to
do today and left a while ago.
You're doing a lot to help the student council out, right?
I see.. So you know that?
She wouldn't tell me what she was doing or anything..
But she did insinuate that she was very busy.
Come on now, if you knew about her
being so busy, why didn't you help her out?
She didn't come and actually ask for help.
You're the one she's relying on.
She's really not, she's just using me.
It's because you can't refuse anyone, huh?
Hey, that's the kind of club I'm in.
I have no reason to refuse
her. Unlike you, I'm mostly free.
Is that right?
What are you trying to say?
Even though it has nothing to do with practice..
You wouldn't have turned her down either.
I dunno know.
I'm really not as good of a guy as you think I am.
I'm counting on you to help her alright?
Isshiki?
Sorry.
Did I keep you waiting for long?
I waited for a while, so I figured I'd look for you.
I think you're supposed to be saying, "No, I
just got here Isshiki"? Come on get with it.
It's not really heavy today, so it's okay.
Are you sure?
Yeah.
It's getting late.. Let's hurry.
We have high hopes for your individual manpower.
But we'll decide together!
So please make suggestions proactively!
We'll do our best president.
You call them here, then neglect them?
Should we go ask what we should be doing?
Who do we ask? I can't do it.
Let's ask the teacher what to do.
Yeah, that's a good idea. I'll go and ask.
What should we do?
We met these kids during summer
vacation when we volunteered at their camp.
I destroyed the human relationships
surrounding Rumi Tsurumi.
I even made Hayama and his
friends play the unlikely villains.
Hey... What's the matter with you?
Nothing to worry about.
What should we do here?
Don't ask me.
Sorry to interrupt.
What should the elementary students to do..
President?
Well..Uh..
We haven't really decided on anything yet.
It's best if we confirm things
with them over there, right?
We said we'd take care of them, remember?
We need to come up with something ourselves.
Right. Yes that's true.
Let's think of a task we need done..
Something that they can't get in the way of.
What about decorations.. Or something along those lines?
Yeah ok.. Let's have them to do that then.
This is okay for the time being,
but we can't build past this point, if
we can't decide what the essentials are.
If she's so hesitant about talking to Tamanawa...
Got a moment?
What's up?
Listen.. If we can't decide on what the events
about, even with help, nothing will get done.
Okay, we'll think of something together.
No way... we won't figure it
out by discussing vague ideas.
I think to start we need to narrow down our list
of things we want to accomplish and then review them.
However..won't that really limit our field of vision here?
I think we should use a method of exploring
for a solution where we can all contribute.
But.. We don't have time.
That's right, we should all get together
and discuss what to do about that, too.
I get why you are in a hurry.. But let's
try to do our best and help everyone out... 'kay?
Ok then.. But that meeting
needs to really happen right now.
No problem. So let's start the meeting right away.
We were able to collaborate together on the ground design,
so I think we should start by discussing
the more creative parts of the event.
We need something that is both Christmas and uniquely us.
Upon further reflection I feel like the classic
Christmas concert is the standard event for this area.
Don't you guys think Jazz is more Christmas-like?
But shouldn't we take the young-minded
into consideration? Like have a band.
We should get a church choir or borrow a pipe organ.
You tell 'em!
Alright. Let's discuss everything one by one.
Isn't it easier to choose from the things they just said?
Instead of rejecting opinions..
We need to accept everyone's proposals
then make something that we can all agree on.
We can't move forward this way...
Some are systematically similar,
so, we should be able to collaborate on this.
What about a Christmas concert that
includes many different genres of music?
If we're looking for a unified solution..
Don't music and musicals go hand in hand together?
Wait, what if we put those two together?
Sort of like a musical movie?
Then I'll take the initiative and...
You go and tell 'em!
Hachiman!
Hey, Hachiman!
Heeey!
The heater is turned up a bit high, isn't it?
It's so... hot.
Weird. Really weird.
Also the heater's the only reason why I'm
blushing. Or it's highly likely I have a cold.
And Totsuka's a boy.
Calm down.
I'll calm down and write a haiku.
Maybe I am sick.
No way! I cannot be sick!
Okay, I am sick.
I'm totally sick, aren't I?
I'm so sick! I'm writing a haiku!
This is delicious.
Hey, you're eating a lot more than usual, aren't you?
Aren't you supposed to eat a lot
food when you're feeling really tired?
Wait you've seemed like you've been kinda tired, lately.
You think so?
Did something happen?
Not really.
Don't worry it's nothing.
That's ok. You wouldn't say anything even if it did, huh?
No, that's not entirely true.
It's just.. I've been very busy helping
Isshiki out with her request on a certain event.
It's more just me supporting her for now.
Really?
Yeah. Don't you worry about me.
Ok then.
You're really cool, huh, Hachiman?
What?
Oh! No no, I don't mean that in a strange way!
I mean.. You really do well on your own.
Even when it's tough for you, you don't whine.
I just think that's really cool of you.
That's not true of me at all.
I actually whine a lot and I complain about everything.
Yeah you probably do.
Really.. Tell me if you need help.
I'm "cool.." huh?
There no way.
I think I'm just purely putting on an act.
I stubbornly cling to these strict ideals that
I've created for myself and have drilled into my mind.
However... Yuigahama's strained smile..
The sullen expression that Isshiki sometimes shows..
And the solitary figure of Rumi Tsurumi,
but.. Most of all, it's the quiet, resigned
smile of Yukinoshita that has only made me wonder.
Is it really as ideal as I thought it was?
Oh hi, what're you doing?
Hey. Are you out buying snacks again?
No. It doesn't seem like there's
going to be a meeting today.
Well, that's too bad.
Yeah, too bad, right?
I guess you won't get to score any points with me.
If scoring points with you is
that simple, I don't need them.
Huh? Hey it's Isshiki and Hikigaya.
Oh hello there.
Sup guys!
That's right, I always forget
you two knew each other from before.
Yeah, we went to the same junior high school.
I'm actually surprised you had any friends at all.
I don't know if I'd say that
but yeah, okay then.
Sounds like there's a story. You have to tell it to me!
Come on.. Tell me the story, will ya?!
Cut it out already it's... complicated.
Well, it's all in the past now, isn't it?
Hey, tell me about it!
Um...
No matter how you calculate it, we are going over budget.
What should we do here?
We need to scale down or find more funding.
We're really going to have to
make a decision in the next meeting.
So um.. It looks like the kids will be
finished with the decorations really soon.
What do you think I should I have them do next?
How 'bout setting up the tree?
Well, the tree is here and ready to be worked on now..
But if we go ahead and put it together,
don't you think it'll be in the way?
How about we ask the center if they
can put it in the entrance for now.
Christmas is next week so might be ok.
We can just move it back to
the venue on the day of the event.
Okay, great I've got it.
This is the wrong way to do this.
I'm the one giving out all the orders.
You can't really call what I'm
doing support or backup for Isshiki.
I need to somehow fix this, so she can take charge
for the rest of it... Thus fulfilling her request.
We thoroughly looked through all the ideas we had,
then sorted them into doable and not.
Most of them look impossible due to the budget, though.
Oh, thank you for doing that.
This makes the issue at hand crystal clear for me.
We shall all come together and
discuss the possible solutions...
We don't have time for this!
We have a week before the event.
Fortunately there are many
options when looking for a band.
If we can come up with the right combination,
we will host a good event.
So, let's refocus and discuss things first.
If we don't make a decision in the next
meeting, nothing will get done in time.
Please keep that in mind.
Of course.
Ugh seriously. This is all over.
Is she making the decorations?
Are you making them all by yourself?
Isn't it obvious?
That was a really delayed response.
What are you doing?
Isn't it obvious?
Don't you have anything better to do?
You know, actually I really don't.
Lazy.
Leave me alone.
I need to borrow the box cutter, ok?
I'm guessing based on what I
see your liking the younger girls?
Well, I can't say I dislike them.
I've got a little sister, after all.
Are you hitting on me?
I'm so sorry, I really like
older guys, but this is impossible.
Oh please, clearly I wasn't hitting on you Isshiki.
Why are you treating me like that?
They're all done, right?
Time to go back then.
Oh... hey Hachiman... Thank you...
So the tree.
I believe they're still working on it..
So why don't you go give 'em a hand?
Uh... yeah.
Even using my old methods,
I did manage to save some things,
but..I'm still not sure if it's enough.
What is my responsibility here?
I haven't found the answer to that question yet.
Hey.
Good evening.
Uh..you were shopping?
Yes.
So what about you? What are you doing out here this late?
I had some things to take care of.
Right.
So tell me... you're helping Isshiki, right?
Yeah. But it's not like I had a choice in it.
You didn't have to lie to me about what you're doing.
I wasn't really lying to you.
Komachi's exams are big.
That's right.
You didn't technically lie to us.
I'm sorry I took her request on my own.
I don't really mind.
Seriously what you do with your free time is your own.
It's not like I have any control what you do.
I don't have a say in your life.
Unless you mean..
You really just need my permission?
No. I just really wanted you to know okay?
I see.
But there's no need to apologize about it, though.
Anyways... I'm sure that Isshiki finds it a
lot easier to work with you rather than all of us.
You're just really good at resolving things by yourself.
It's always been like that.
I haven't really resolved anything.
Also, I only do things alone because I am alone.
Aren't you the same?
Actually I'm...
not like that.
I always act like I could do anything,
like I totally understand everything.
That's not true, Yukinoshita...
How about taking a break from the club?
If you're there trying to watch over
us.. You're really just wasting your time.
I'm really not, that's not my intention here.
But you are doing that.
And you've done it since the beginning.
So, that's why..
It's fine.. If you stop forcing
yourself just for our sake.
If we can be torn apart this
easy.. We weren't close to begin with.
Am I wrong?
So.. See ya around ok?
We really need to confirm the agenda for the next meeting.
Wow, an agenda? That's like super important, isn't it?
We'll then share the updated agenda through the cloud.
The cloud! That sounds so powerful!
We should upload a digest as well.
A digest? Sounds delicious!
Take a decent buffer...
Buffer? I'm down with that!
Okay. I think, we've got it.
So, let us all brainstorm and then commit to the results.
Commit to the results!
You tell 'em!
So.. What're we discussing?