About the other day... I'm sorry.
No problem!
My mom is always trying to tell me
that I stay out much too late, too.
Yeah... that's what moms are supposed to do.
They're always complaining about something.
And with the entrance exams coming up and all,
Komachi and our mom have really been going at each other.
Oh that's right, Komachi has her exams tomorrow.
We even get the whole day off because of it.
Knowing Komachi, I think she's going
to end up being just fine tomorrow.
Yeah.
But as her big brother, you must be worried, right?
I find that I am.
I mean, Komachi's really cute,
so she'll surely be popular.
That means she'll have to be careful around guys,
and she'll need to be sure to keep people from
finding out about her useless, no good, worthless brother.
It would surely ruin her good reputation.
THAT'S what you're worried about now?
You act like she's already passed!
Are you trying to be positive
or negative? I can't really tell?
Oh! Yukinon? Did you make those cookies yourself?
Uh... yeah.
In fact I baked up this batch of cookies last night.
That sounds nice.
I've been trying really hard with baking cookies.
But I'm still struggling.
These cookies are for you.
Wow! Thank you so much!
But, uh... Is this all for me?
Why am I looking away?
What about Hikki?
You can have some.
Uh... Thank you.
See ya.
Yeah, later!
Uh...
Well, um...
So uh... Yeah.. I'm gonna head on out now!
So then, uh...
Well... what should we do now?
Yukino... I'm here to pick you up.
Sis?
I don't think there is any need
for you to come and pick me up.
Mom told me to stay with you for now.
So you better do what she says, okay?
Why is this happening all of a sudden?
Really? I think you know why.
Well, it's just, that's something I have to do myself.
It has nothing to do with you.
Do you even you have a so-called "self"?
You've just been following in my footsteps up until now.
Do you even think on your own?
You've always been free to do as
you please in your own built castle,
but you've never decided anything on your own.
Even now, you don't know how to act.
What exactly is it? What do you want to do?
Do you think that you could
possibly do this fight somewhere else?
I don't think this is a fight where having now.
After all, we've never had any kind of fight before.
Well, either way.. This isn't
a discussion to have in public.
Yeah... so... we are thinking about it...
Both Yukinon... and me, too.
Oh? Yeah? Well, tell me about it when you get home.
I mean, it's not like you have anywhere else to go?
It's just you and me.
Umm... uhh... so, uh.. Oh, yeah! Wanna come over?
I came along with them without a second thought...
I'm sorry, guys. I didn't mean to cause you trouble.
Not at all. Don't worry.
That's right! Don't worry about anything at all, my dear!
So you must be, Hikki... right?
Yeah.
Yui has told me so much about you.
Mother! You don't have to tell him that!
But I want to talk to Hikki and get to know him, too!
You don't have to!
Oh, I know. Yukino's staying over, right?
She'll need a futon and clean sheets.
I'll take care of that!
Sorry about my mom and all.
She's really happy you came over.
She doesn't usually get this excited...
I'm so embarrassed.
It's alright.
You two are close, huh? I'm a little jealous of that.
With family like that, it'd be hard for anyone, let
alone Yukinoshita, to have a good relationship with them.
I'm sorry. I shouldn't have said something like that.
I think I'll be leaving now.
Oh, I was actually just thinking why don't you stay?
But I couldn't...
You have me sleep over at your house all the time...
and I don't think you want to go home.
Plus, I bet you wouldn't be able
to talk it out peacefully right now.
Why don't you spend the night here
so you can at least think it over?
But still let your sister know, just in case.
Yeah. You should do that.
Okay, then. I guess you're both right about that.
Hello, sis?
I don't think we'll be able to
talk this out peacefully tonight.
I'm going to spend the night thinking it over.
I'm letting you know, just in case.
Oh? Okay.
Hikigaya is with you too, right? Give him the phone.
Here go Hikki... she wants to talk to you.
What is it?
You know... You're always so nice, Hikigaya.
Are you still awake?
Yeah.
What do you wanna do... Yukinon?
I don't know...
Well, I do know... just what I wanna do...
I've made up my mind.
Tomorrow, will you go on a date with me?
I'm sorry?
It's so cold!
You have your exam ID?
And an eraser and handkerchief? And an extra pencil?
I've got it.
I'm on my way, then, big bro!
Kay. Be careful out there.
Sine, cosine, tangent...
Looks like it's gonna snow all day.
Hikki, let's go on a date!
What?!
If I'm in the way here, I can
leave... It's no problem at all.
It's... fine.
Seriously you guys... I want us to be together.
The Sea Life Park?
Is this really okay?
Yeah! We don't have to worry about snow in here.
Yay! Sharks!
Sharks, huh?
Yukinon! Sorry I didn't tell you earlier.
We should get more excited, okay?!
Easier said than done.
Whoa... look at all those hammerhead sharks!
Wait so you're allowed to take pictures in here?
See? Hikki is having fun here, too!
Wh-what?
Nothing, I was just a little surprised is all.
How about... I take a picture with you and the sharks.
Really? Komachi's gonna be so jealous.
It says it's a nurseryfish.
They live in muddy streams but don't swim much.
They're known for carrying their
egg clusters on forehead hooks.
So cool.
Yeah.
And they get to eat shrimp and
whatever else that passes them by.
They really live the perfect life.
You're envious of that?!
Wow, now that I've really taken a
look at it, this fish resembles someone.
Isn't that right Fishigaya?
Hey, we're nothing alike and leave my name out of it.
Ew... Gross... nasty!
You shouldn't say means things like that.
They're doing their best to survive.
Alright well I guess they're kinda cute.
Well, I don't know if you can call them cute,
but they certainly are charming.
You can't exactly call them "cute"
if you've already established them as "gross."
Ooh, a dogfish shark!
It kinda looks like Sable!
How's that?
A catshark? That makes no sense.
They must be like cats in some
way if they've taken their name.
She reacts to anything with cat in its name, huh?
She really does love cats. How frisky.
It kinda feels like a cat's tongue when I touch it.
That's shark skin.
Ah, there's a ray, too.
Oh gross! I just felt something that was super slimy!
What did you touch? Was it Hikigaya?
You should hurry and go wash your hands.
Could you stop treating me like that? I'm not a ray, okay?
Cat... Catshark... Cat... Meow.
Or... shaa maybe?
Just because it's a shark does not mean it goes shaa.
That's it? You done already?
Mhm. It wouldn't be fair to tire them out
because I'm touching them too much.
I see. Well that's very you.
And what exactly do you mean by "very me", Hikki?
I bet you have an idea of me in your mind
but I'm not as nice of a girl as you think.
Ah Penguins!
Come on guys we've gotta go see em!
Oh wow, they're so disgustingly cute!
I need to get a picture of this for Komachi.
Look... look how they're swimming.. Isn't that so cute?
Seeing them like this makes you
think they're kind of like birds, huh?
Uh Penguins are actually birds Yuigahama.
I knew that.
What's up?
I'm gonna go wait inside.
Where's Yuigahama?
She's taking pictures of the fairy penguins.
Kay.
Some of them are left to themselves.
Yeah... that one is pretty big, after all.
Always unable to find a place to
belong without a pillar of support...
Hiding in the crowd, going with the flow...
following everyone else's paths...
until it runs into an unseen wall.
Which fish are you talking about?
Myself.
Sorry to keep you waiting!
Oh wow... they look like fireworks, huh?
You think so?
Don't you? That one over there.
"Frooom... pop!"
Too close.
I'm glad we did this.
Together.
Done!
Unless.. You wanna do it again?
No, that's ok. No point in seeing
the same places more than once.
Y-yeah. I'm a bit tired now.
Aw, really? I think it'd be fun.
I mean, we still have some time. Don't we?
Hiding its instability... it continues to turn so slowly.
Instead of making any progress...
it just keeps going around in circles.
Even so... eventually...
Seems to be... almost done.
What are we gonna do now?
Go home?
That's not what I meant.
- About Yukinon. - Also... me.
And about us.
I'm confused... what do you mean?
Hikki.
Here.
As thanks for way back when.
Do you remember... my request?
Homemade cookies? You made these all by yourself?
I did, but messed up on them a bit.
You're incredible... I'm proud.. Yuigahama.
Do you remember when I told you I'd try to do it myself...
and do it my own way without
trying to be like other people?
So this is how they turned out.
These are... a thanks for that.
You already paid me back for that.
Even so,
they're a token of my thanks.
To be honest I want it all.
What is now, and what will be in the future.
But that's just me being unfair. I'm also a coward.
However, I've made up my mind on this.
I see...
I worry that if we figure out how we feel about things,
we might not be able to keep things how they are.
So now... this is my new final request.
Our task is to fix our problems.
Do you think we can do that?
Hey Yukinon... is that battle still going on in our club?
Yes. The winner can make the loser do anything they want.
I think I know how to solve the problem you have
right now... I mean at least I think I do, Yukinon.
However I believe it's the same
solution to our problem as well.
So, when I win... I'm going to take it all, okay?
She didn't actually come out and
say anything really specific here.
Putting it into words would confirm it for all of us...
so she kept avoiding it.
It's probably not fair, but
this is all I could come up with.
I want us to stay this way forever.
What do you think?
Yuigahama isn't wrong about this.
I have a feeling she was the only one
looking at the right answers from the beginning.
Accepting her proposal would
make things easier for all of us.
But...
Yukinon... Is that okay with you?
Well... I...
No... this is wrong. She's making a mistake.
I... don't want...
Letting Yukinoshita leave her
future in someone else's hands,
is in no way okay here.
I just...
I think...
I think I would be okay with...
No.
I can't accept your proposal.
This isn't being fair to her.
Yukinoshita needs to solve this on her own.
"Yui Yuigahama... is a nice girl."
I decided that without even thinking of the truth.
"Yukino Yukinoshita... is a strong girl."
So I burdened her with the ideal image I had of her.
Besides... that proposal's just...
One big lie.
I don't want vague answers. Or
any superficial relationships.
I'm totally serious... I don't want that.
I'm know I'm being stupid.
And I know it'll never be that way.
And I know how this will end.
I'll end up being left with nothing again.
Even so... I want us to think...
to suffer... And struggle...
And I...
You know... I thought you'd say that.
You do not get to decide how I feel here.
Anyways... this isn't the last request.
Hikigaya...
We still have your request, right?
Even if we're wrong, it's okay...
Because every time we are wrong,
we will continue to look for the right answer.
Oh... one more thing...
I have a request.
Can I tell you what it is?
Sure. Let's hear it.