- Did you need something? - I mean, you called me here.
I was thinking we could compare
our answers as we said we would.
Did you ask Yukino about her plans?
I know we agreed to that but I don't think
it's fair of me to be the one to tell you.
My what a loyal friend!
I see how it is.. She really
did tell you her plans didn't she?
Wow. So Yukino really does trusts you a great deal huh?
I don't know if it's really trust.
I'm not really very trustworthy.
Oh, so you already know that then?
Right. It's not really trust per se.
It's something much worse.
She hasn't changed at all.
And she actually thinks that this is okay.
I suppose that's a fairly cute thing about her, but...
I don't like this one little bit.
If it isn't trust, then what is it?
Well... At the very least, it's
something that can't be called genuine.
That was your word, huh?
Does something like "genuine"... really ever exist?
Man... I'm really wanting to
eat something sweet... ya know?
Don't you guys?
Yummy chocolate?
Just a bit? Just a bit o' choco?
That's right it's coming up soon.
You'll be fine though, Hayato.
The rest of us are in trouble.
That's true except Hayato won't really accept
any Valentine's chocolates this year, right?
For real?! What a waste!
I get it though. I mean isn't it kinda scary to
get chocolates from someone you don't really know?
Well, handmade ones are a bit too serious, right?
Serious?
Sure that's right... I guess.
Just some chocolate! Just one thing, a chocolate, please!
Just a little bit'a chocolate!
Handmade... huh?
Hey. Why'd you just leave me behind?
I've never implied that we'd always go to club together.
Well I just thought you would just wait for me, Hikki.
Since you stayed in the classroom for a while and all.
Well... Hayama and Miura seemed to be a bit better.
Yeah... seems like everything's fine again.
Everything's going pretty great, right? You know,
it's like they're really trying to treasure this moment.
Or they think now is the best time...
Yeah maybe.
There's probably no better time than now.
Whoa! It's a very rare positive thought from Hikki!
Well the past just makes you want to die from regret
and thoughts of the future
makes you depressed with anxiety.
So process of elimination, now is the best time.
Never mind! It was negative!
I guess things never change...
So, hey there... Will you be free anytime soon?
Huh?! Well, uh... Yeah. I mean... I probably am.
I'm generally mostly free... but it's just I...
I'm gonna think on it a bit.
O-Okay.
Yahallo!
Hikigaya you're late!
Isshiki, what are you even doing here?
Anyways... I don't really care by the
way, but do you happen to like sweets?
Ya know I'm pretty sure that
Hayama would be happy to eat whatever.
I think Hayama actually said he
wasn't accepting any chocolates.
What? Why is that?! Don't know.
Because it would obviously lead to conflict.
Back in elementary school, the classroom always had
a more strained atmosphere the day after Valentines.
Well... I guess I'll just have to settle for you.
Does someone like you enjoy sweet stuff?
That's a weird question, isn't it?
Hikki just...
he just really really loves sweets!
He honestly does.
I don't actually know why you two had to answer for him,
but if so, then that's perfect!
What are you talking about?
Well I wasn't actually sure how
sweet I should be making the chocolate.
I mean everyone really has different preferences, right?
Making chocolate huh?
So your saying you plan on making these candies yourself?
I'm surprised.
Why would you say that?!
I'm really quite good at making sweets!
Anyway, I just want to ask your opinion on
the chocolate I'm making out of obligation.
Obligation?
Oh what? Are you the type who's never
actually gotten chocolate before?
Hikki...
will be getting chocolates for sure.
Right?
Huh? Do you mean...
Heh. That's right.
I've got Komachi, after all.
Komachi? What is that? A rice? She's not a rice.
Komachi is actually Hikki's way cooler little sister.
Your sister?
You're such a moron.
I dunno if I can actually deny that though.
So you really are into younger girls after all, huh?
That isn't true.
And besides that, your birthday's in April,
so there's less than a year's difference.
You don't really feel like a younger girl at all.
What?
Oh, nothing.
I was a bit surprised, that's all.
Weird! Why do you know her birthday?!
You're being creepy, Hikki! Seriously creepy.
You're pretty well informed there.
You know, you were there when she brought it up herself.
You were pointlessly trying to be sly, weren't you?
Pointless... It wasn't pointless at all!
And I'm not sly! If anything, you're
the one being sly here! So stop being mean.
Well actually,
I was kinda thinking... I wanna try making some chocolate.
I mean why not? Next year we have exams.
So I figured I should go ahead
and give it a try now, right?
It's now or never.
Wait didn't you say handmade chocolate is way too serious?
W-well yes but...
You know what I happen to think
is actually a really good idea.
Hikitani you should def give
Hayato some good buddy chocolates!
Nope I don't think so.
I mean it's not like he's gonna accept them anyway.
I bet he would if it was from another guy.
Why would a guy do that on Valentine's?
Yeah why would he do that?
If he says he's not accepting any,
that makes things a lot more difficult.
It really does.
Wow... they're quite scary.
Well... did you need something?
Uh, well...
Hey can't you see that I was actually
here first and I'm not done talking?
Yeah? All I see is you drinking tea.
What?
Hey come on now. I'm sure Sakisaki
had a reason to come here, too.
I think we should all hear her out now.
Well it's... its about chocolate as well.
Really you're gonna give someone
chocolates? That's hilarious.
Yeah?
Yeah!
I'm not like you. So you can go
quit acting all high and mighty.
Yeah?
Yeah!
Stop it! Play nice!
Kay... what about chocolate?
My little sister wants to try and make some.
Is there anything with chocolate
even a little kid can make?
Something a little kid can make?
But Sakisaki... I thought you were good at home ec stuff.
Well I can cook a bit, but the
stuff I make is really plain.
I don't really think it's something a kid would like much.
So what kind of stuff can you make, by the way?
Boi-Boiled...
I can make boiled sweet potatoes.
Yep, that's plain.
I think that's pretty good!
I can't cook anything at all, so I think that
makes you really quite awesome! Right... Yukinon?
Indeed.
I think that totally sounds like something cats would
really love. I really think cats loving things is so cute.
Come on is that the best you can do here?!
Cats have nothing to do with this.
This is quite a problem.
Yeah. Miura is really pulling out all the stops
and I'm getting worried that I can't keep up with her.
That's true, but I was actually talking
about the number of requests coming in.
I feel bad... but I kinda get how Hayama feels about this.
Oh, wait that's not what I really meant here.
I meant he's popular so he's gotta think of
other's feelings and is looking out for that.
Yeah, I think that kinda sounds a bit like you.
Really you think so?
So just like me... huh?
Well... all we need is an excuse.
Like a reason for Hayato to accept it.
Huh?
A situation where he has to take it.
Or, one where taking it is the obvious course of action.
Okay... so you're saying we
need to come up with an excuse?
For example... instead of a grand gesture,
if you just asked him to test it, he probably would.
Not that I really know.
Hey I know, why don't we all just make some together?
Yeah that is an excellent idea!
Get everyone who asked for help and make an event!
Then you can offer a masterclass
and teach everyone at the same time.
Uh, sure. I actually wouldn't mind doing that.
Uh, vice president?
I need you to draw up and submit a proposal!
So what can I do?
Well let's see, how about you...
just come and work as my partner.
You don't believe in me at all!
So, uh, what will Hikki do then in the class?
Nope, I absolutely cannot cook.
That's okay.
You only need to taste the chocolate
and then give us your thoughts.
You're asking the right person. I am very good at that.
Okay, I'm counting on you.
Okay that's set.
The student council will handle all the details,
Alrighty then you guys, go put on a great class.
So... our last event was very well-received.
We garnered a lot of attention. I'd really like
the opportunity to keep our alliance going strong.
That sounds great!
Oh... I see you guys are here, as well.
Oh, didn't I tell you they were coming?
I'm afraid I don't remember seeing
it in our most recent text exchange...
Oh, man. You're so cute!
We'd like to go ahead and get started, Mr. President.
Great. See you later.
This is also a chance at business...
What are they doing here, Isshiki?
I figured we could get some funds from
them by collaborating. Isn't that for the best?
And it'd be great for me if I
didn't have to spend my own money.
O-okay.
Well let's put that thought aside for now,
You hide it but you know you're quite capable, Isshiki.
Yahallo!
Sister...
Sorry I was running so late, you guys!
Looks it's Miss Haruno, she's going
to be our special lecturer for today!
Oh Hello there, I'm Miss Haruno!
And WHY did you call her here?
Because she seems really experienced
and I thought we needed that, right?
I could've done this by myself.
Cut up the chocolate and boil it in water.
Once it cools down, then pour it into a mold.
Is that it?
Yeah, that's about it more or less.
Huh. That sounds so easy.
Don't be so naive!
There's so much more than just boiling water
and simply adding chocolate!
You gotta do it like BAM! And then POW kay?
Was it really okay to bring her along?
Don't know why it wouldn't be.
Thank you. All right Kei, what
kind of candy would you like to eat?
Eel please!
Uh... uh, well... okay then.
Sorry!
We had that for dinner just the other night.
She loved it and has asked for it ever since.
Overseas, it's more common for
men to give gifts on Valentine's.
So, we should keep that
globalization in mind for this event.
This was a really good idea.
With it this way, everyone can act normal.
And Tobe's really excited about it, too.
Choco!
I really don't care much about chocolate or Tobe.
Mainly Tobe.
That's a little harsh.
Hayato!
Wow... You're really good at this, huh?
Are you hitting on me again?
Thinking that whispering sweet words to me would
work just because I'm making sweets is cute, but foolish.
I'm sorry but, please try again later.
Here!
So tell me, is it way too sweet for you or what?
You must remember that there is quite a difference between
Japanese and overseas mindsets when it comes to sweets.
You could call it a culture gap.
Do you have any extra chocolate molds, Hikigaya?
Uh, yeah.
Thanks, these are perfect!
Come to think of it, didn't I
give you Valentine chocolate once?
No, never.
Then I'll give you some this year.
Uh, okay.
That reminds me! You got some from
Yukino before, didn't you, Hayato?
Yeah... I did.
It was before we started elementary school.
I believe you got some too, Haruno.
So... who are you planning to give chocolate to?
Well that's actually not any of your business now is it?
Interesting you're not telling me nobody?
Which leads me to believe someone is getting some.
Well, there's only a few guys
you'd even consider giving chocolate.
That's ridiculous. You can say what...
I-I'm so sorry!
It's fine...
Why are you getting so flustered?
Looking at you like that makes me get flustered, too.
Do not get... flustered.
You still have a way to go, Yukinon.
My special ability to handle
bowls and utensils is top notch.
That may be true for this, but you're
still hopeless at everything else.
Well this turned out to be a great event.
It did. Though for a school event it was pretty weird.
You know what, that's okay.
Because you're actually a pretty weird guy as well.
Take a look around. Everyone here is kind of weird.
Of course, this would end up weird.
Don't you think you're being a little mean?
No... but I do believe I understand you a bit better now.
People's perception of others
tend to get clearer day by day.
If you continue to spend time
with someone and grow with them,
you'll eventually understand them.
I don't feel like we've really
grown this year at all, y'know?
We just always seem to be doing the same thing.
People usually don't look back to see how far
they've come while they're still walking forward.
Of course though, when they come
to a stop they look behind them,
and the more progress they've made, the
more betrayed they feel by their expectations.
Honestly for me, I'm glad I
was able to see this personally.
But I can't continue watching over you guys forever.
Hikki, will you please give these a try for me?
Kay... fine.
You really seem to be preparing
for the absolute worst Hikigaya,
you don't need to worry, I worked on them as well.
Good, it's a relief to know I won't die.
You don't have to be mean about it!
Hmm, well...
Thanks for that.
Sure!
Huh. Is this what you're calling genuine?
Are these the kinds of things you feel are genuine to you?
I can't really say for sure.
Is this really it?
I thought you guys were better than that.
Are you really this boring Hikigaya?
I'd be the most popular guy in
class if I were slightly interesting.
I really like that about you.
But right now, you guys are seriously...
pretty boring here.
You know what? I actually prefer
the old Yukino to the new one.
All of this was so new to me,
and I'd never experienced anything like it,
I thought... I just wasn't used to this sort of thing yet.
I actually figured
I'd eventually learn to live with it.
But... she still saw right through all of us.
The student council can take
care of things, you guys can leave.
Oh... we don't mind staying and helping until the end.
Yeah, you don't have to always be so polite with us.
If you're really sure?
I'll gladly take you up on that offer.
Haruno Yukinoshita had really made something obvious...
something I was trying not to think about.
She said it wasn't trust,
but something else which was much worse than that.
Mother? Why are you here?
Haruno told me all about your career
plans, and I wanted to talk to you.
Yukino, what in the world are
you doing traipsing around so late?
You know, I've never actually expected
this type of behavior to come from you.
I put my trust in you and let
you do as you wanted, but now...
No... I can only blame myself. This is my mistake.
Please tell me where I went so wrong?
Um...
there was a student council event at school
today and we stayed late so we could clean up.
I see. And you walked her home
afterwards? I appreciate it.
But you really shouldn't be staying out so late...
you do that and your family is
bound to start worrying. Right?
I want you to stay true to
yourself and live a life of freedom,
But I'm a bit worried with so much freedom
you may end up going down the wrong path.
I will explain.
But please go home now.
True to herself? True to myself?
We all have our own personal image
that others try and dictate for us...
one that is always slightly off.
We want to remain true to ourselves,
but who gets to decide that?
Who gets to control who we are as people?
Um, I'm gonna... head home now.
Oh, I'll walk you.
It's okay.
I feel like that'd be unfair.
Okay.
When our image never really matches with reality...
Where can we find... something genuine?
Where can we find our true selves?
There's something I want, but I'm not very smart
and I don't play fair, so I only know one answer.
But I'm sure that's not the
answer someone would expect of me.
Why is it that what I want and what's expected of me
are always so similar...
but at the same time so different?
Honestly, I'd be happy with a lie.