[IKUYA] Why didn't you
say anything to me?
[HARUKA]
It's the same.
Because I, uh...
[alarm beeping]
[HARUKA] Weird. Why'd I
dream about back then?
[doorbell rings]
[MAKOTO]
Good morning, Haru.
Yeah. Morning.
Well, are you ready to head out?
[MAKOTO panting]
After that,
Nagisa just kept on
eating even more.
[HARUKA]
Sounds exactly like him.
[MAKOTO] Yeah, but then after
that, he got a personal best.
[HARUKA]
Yeah.
Whats wrong? You cold?
The wind is cold.
I guess it is a
little chilly, huh?
[HARUKA]
Even though it's already spring.
Yeah. It's like there's only
a hint of spring in the air.
This time of year always
reminds me of stuff, you know?
I can't help it.
Like, do you remember
the first day we met?
[BOY A]
Whoa, a dump truck!
Really? Oh!
[BOY A]
Whoa, it's so huge!
Wait for me!
Are you all right?
[MAKOTO] Truth is, I've
always felt pretty lucky
to have met you that day.
You're a really
great friend, Haruka.
We've agreed not to call
me that, haven't we?
[NAGISA]
Haru! Mako!
[MAKOTO]
Hey, Nagisa! Hey, Rei!
[chuckles]
You guys are early.
[REI] Well, spring break
is almost over.
I can't stop imagining
school in April
and getting to
demonstrate the new me.
Who could ever sleep in
when there's this much
showing off to anticipate?
Good point. Wow, Rei,
you're fired up.
I for one, am just excited
about all the stamina
I'm building on these long runs!
[chuckles] Wow, you two
are so dependable.
Thanks!
All I want in the whole
world is the four of us
to get as far as we
can this coming year.
So, which way should we go?
Do we get to take
the usual route?
Sure thing. I'm
ready if you are.
[NAGISA] In that case,
good luck catching up,
'cause I'm takin' the lead!
Hey! That's not fair!
You realize this is cheating!
C'mon, guess we can't
just stand here.
[GOU] So that's our official
plan for recruiting
new students to the club!
We're gonna get everyone's
attention with this.
Trust me! It won't be long
before we'll have fresh,
new members who'll have
the best muscles ever!
[ALL]
Yeah!
[GOU] And now, we will
introduce the members
of the Iwatobi Swim Club!
Our treasurer!
[STUDENTS gasp]
[NAGISA]
Nagisa Hazuki, Second Year!
Breaststroke is my fave and
my best feature is my soleus.
Ladies.
[GOU]
Vice Captain!
[STUDENTS gasp]
[HARUKA]
Haruka Nanase, Third Year!
Freestyle is my thing,
and my triceps are guaranteed
to drive you out of your mind.
[GOU]
Secretary!
[REI]
Ha!
Rei Ryugazaki, Second Year!
Butterfly expert, who when
asked his best feature,
will answer that his deltoids
and biceps are in a dead heat.
[GOU]
And our team captain!
[STUDENTS murmur]
[MAKOTO]
Makoto Tachibana, Third Year!
I've got backstroke for days!
And traps just as long!
[GOU] Join us, and become
a more muscular you!
No one's here!
This sucks.
I thought someone would've
shown up for sure.
Well, it doesn't matter
how strong we are at running,
we're still only a Swim Club.
[SASABE] Really? That's
unusual coming from Haruka.
Aw, thank you so much for this.
[SASABE]
You think this means the kid
might be starting to mature?
Maybe.
But, to be honest,
I was surprised with him
at the race last year, also.
It seems like Nanase
and the others
have something in mind.
[AMAKATA]
They're good boys.
You know, it's funny. I've
had such a difficult time
figuring out the best way to
help as their faculty advisor,
yet I feel like they always
know how to encourage me.
[SASABE] A lot's happened
in the past few years.
I'm just glad he's found
a way to approach swimming
that keeps him true to himself
while also maintaining
his talent.
He's been fussy about
swimming freestyle
since he was little. At least
he's good at it, I guess.
[AMAKATA]
Oh, kids that age.
They grow every day,
and in so many ways.
Adolescence is great,
don't you agree?
[SASABE]
Hm. Haruka's already year three.
That's right, yeah?
I wonder if he or Makoto
have given a single thought
to their futures at all.
[AMAKATA] Probably. Look how
hard they're working now.
If they put even half the
effort into their futures
as they do swimming,
they'll be just fine.
Hopefully you're
right about that.
[RIN]
Hey, uh. You guys.
You ever give any thought
to life after graduation?
Not really.
So you have no idea
what you're gonna do?
[laughs] We can't all have our
sights set as high as you.
[RIN]
You're kidding, right?
I've wasted so much time
it's not even funny.
The Nationals this summer are
my last shot at being scouted.
They'll be comin' from all over.
I need to batten down.
Focus on bringin' my A-game.
[RIN]
But seriously, though.
What're gonna do once
high school's just a memory?
[thunder rolls]
Wish I could say.
Truth is, I haven't decided.
[RIN]
How can you not have a plan?
[RIN] Okay, well, since
it's a city tournament,
I guess we won't
make it mandatory
--for everyone on the team to--
--[NAGISA] Rin!
[laughs]
Ugh.
As I was saying, you don't
have to go if you don't want,
but it'd put some
experience under your belt.
Give it some thought.
[CLUB MEMBERS]
Right!
[REI]
What do ya know.
The man makes a decent
captain after all.
"Rawr! Do or die, maggots!
Take no prisoners!"
That's my impression of what
he thinks he sounds like.
Now, that's not very nice.
[SASABE]
You're late!
[NAGISA]
Whoa!
Why're you suited up, coach?
Ha! 'Cause! There's a
gen pop category, too!
[AMAKATA] It's a much
more relaxed atmosphere
than the Regionals.
Rather nice, if you ask me.
If you go for paunches
and underdeveloped
muscles maybe.
Shame there's no relay for us
to showcase our teamwork.
Yeah, kinda sucks.
But, there'll be relays
in the Regionals, though.
[HARUKA] Hey, You hanging out
for the heck of it, or what?
Just waitin' on you.
[RIN] We're in lanes next
to each other again.
[HARUKA]
I saw.
[RIN] Listen, since you guys
can't train in the winter,
it's only fair if I
give you a handicap.
Just say the word.
I want this race
to be interesting.
[HARUKA]
We don't need your charity.
There are ways to
train without a pool.
[laughs] Sounds like an
intense off-season regimen.
You'll have to show it to me.
--If you can catch up--
--[BOY 1B] You ready to go down?
[BOY 1C]
In your dreams, loser!
[BOY 1B]
Hey, come back here!
[BOYS laughing]
[BOTH chuckle]
[RIN]
No relay in this one, buddy.
Just you and me, head to head.
It's not like I'm worried
about setting a record.
Still tryin' to play it off
like you don't really care?
[RIN] Whatever. Keep
tellin' yourself that.
You may not care about wining,
but you still think
you're the best.
[RIN] You're too cool
for your own good.
I'm gonna light
a fire under you.
--[whistle blowing]
--[NAGISA] Nice.
Rin and Haru are up next.
[GOU]
C'mon, big bro!
[MAKOTO]
Haru!
[REI]
You got this!
[REFEREE 1A]
Ready.
[whistle blows]
Oh, wow, look how fast they are!
[MAKOTO]
Rin's gaining the lead. Fast.
Don't get left behind, Haru!
--[REI] Push, push, push!
--[MAKOTO] C'mon!
[REI] They're on a whole
other level than the rest.
Aw, man!
Haru sure is giving Rin
a run for his money!
They got the same time?
Incredible!
[ANNOUNCER 1A]
Congratulations to the swimmers
in lanes four and five!
Nanase and Matsuoka have set
our first tournament record!
[RIN]
Haru.
See, I knew you had it in you.
You just needed fire.
Whatever you say.
[HARUKA] I feel like
running up the coast today.
[MAKOTO]
Cool. Today's warm.
Plus, we can
increase our stamina
to prepare for Regionals.
[HARUKA]
Right.
[MAKOTO]
Hey, so, uh...
[HARUKA]
Yeah?
[MAKOTO] What'cha got waitin'
for you after all this?
[HARUKA]
What do you mean?
[MAKOTO]
Y'know, what Rin was saying.
What're you gonna do once
high school's just a memory?
[HARUKA] Doesn't matter to me,
as long as I can swim.
[laughs]
[MAKOTO]
Figures.
Listen up, people,
we're down to the wire.
District!
That means you need
plenty of beauty sleep.
You got it?
We'll meet up in front of
registration at 8am sharp.
Come late and I end you.
Are we ready?
Oh-ho yeah! This
one's in the bag!
Even picked ourselves up some
awesome matching swimsuits!
[MAKOTO chuckles]
Yes we did.
What do you say we go over the
program one more time, guys?
First day of District will
be the individual races.
Second's relay.
For the indies, looks
like we have Nagisa
on the 100-meter breaststroke.
Yep!
[MAKOTO]
Rei on 100-meter butterfly.
Of course.
[MAKOTO] Haru on the 100
and 200-meter freestyle.
And as for me, I've got
the 100-meter backstroke,
plus the 200-meter freestyle.
[AMAKATA]
Am I missing something?
If you're doing
freestyle with Haru,
why not the 100-meter?
'Cause he'll kick my butt.
I need the laps
just to stay on him.
Yeah, right.
Someone's being
overly modest. C'mon!
You've been muscling up
your freestyle for weeks.
Our friend here will have his
work cut out for him either way.
It'll take more training than
that to compete with Haru.
I think the 200 meter
will be more my speed.
[MAKOTO]
Haru.
I'm gonna need a favor.
[ANNOUNCER 6A]
Men's 100-meter breaststroke.
Group Three.
It's all you, Nagisa.
Show 'em how it's done.
[whistle blowing]
[REFEREE 6A]
Ready.
[beep]
Let's go! Let's go!
Let's go, Nagisa!
[IWATOBI CLUB] Let's go!
Let's go! Let's go! Let's go!
Let's go, Nagisa!
[SASABE] Push it! Push it!
Push it! Push it!
Push it, Nagisa!
[IWATOBI CLUB] Push it!
Push it! Push it! Push it!
Push it, Nagisa!
[SAMEZUKA, IWATOBI CLUB]
One down!
Hey-hey! Our boy's in the lead!
Somebody's closing
in on him fast!
No, it's okay.
He always holds back
till the end.
Give it a sec--you'll
see what I mean.
[gasps]
[applause]
[REI]
Yes! He did it!
Nagisa made it past the prelims!
Way to go, Nag!
[SASABE]
That's right, you da man! Yeah!
All righty! Backstroke,
time! Come on!
Let's get out there
and make some losers!
Sir!
[ANNOUNCER 6A]
Next up, we have the men's
100-meter backstroke.
[whistle blows]
[REFEREE 6A]
Ready.
--[beep]
--[CROWD] Go!
Let's go! Let's go!
Let's go, Makoto!
[IWATOBI CLUB] Let's go!
Let's go! Let's go! Let's go!
Let's go, Makoto!
[SASABE] Push it! Push it!
Push it! Push it!
Push it, Makoto!
[NAGISA]
Mako's so fast!
[gasps]
Excellent! That's two of us
that've made it through
the preliminaries!
[NAGISA, GOU]
Yay, Makoto!
The time is now ripe.
I shall make my appearance!
Let him sit and watch
while I demonstrate
the superlative sportsmanship
he's chooses to shun!
He keeps talking like that,
he's gonna jinx
himself big time.
[whistle blowing]
[REFEREE 6A]
Ready.
--[beep]
--[CROWD] Go!
[gasps]
[GOU] Nice! Even bellowing
like an ego-maniac,
you cleared District.
[NAGISA]
Because he's amazing!
[REI] Thank you.
That means a lot to me.
I worked so hard
[AMAKATA]
Tachibana, Hazuki, Ryugazaki.
Bravo to all of you!
It must feel wonderful,
knowing you're on your
way to Regionals!
All we need now is for Haru
to place in freestyle.
Ha! You gotta be kidding me!
He could win
freestyle blindfolded!
Makoto, you're swimmin'
the freestyle, too, right?
Two hundred?
Wouldn't miss it.
[NAGISA]
I can't wait!
[GOU] Hey, don't forget
that Haru still has a race
with my brother, too.
I can't wait for that.
[MAKOTO]
Hey.
Remember our talk.
Yeah, no worries.
Wait, those two are racing
against each other?
[whistle blowing]
[REFEREE 6A]
Ready.
--[beep]
--[CROWD] Go!
[GOU] Am I seeing things or did
Makoto just pass everyone?
He's taken the lead!
Since when is he
faster than Haru?
[RIN] Idiot, slow down.
Just pace yourself.
You'll run outta steam
'fore you hit the final lap.
This ain't the 100-meter.
Seriously, where you gonna
be in the second half
if you go all out in the first?
[MAKOTO]
Haru. I'm gonna need a favor.
I want you to swim against me
with everything you've got.
No holding back.
I need this to be legit.
But, why?
Is this the whole reason you're
doing freestyle tomorrow?
So you can try to beat me?
[MAKOTO]
This is our last year.
I mean, once it's
over, it's over.
[MAKOTO]
So before we graduate...
I just... I want one
all-out race against you.
What do you get out
of this? Why do you swim?
Because it's fun.
Because it's--it's something
we do together as a team.
[MAKOTO] But... I wanna know
what it feels like to beat you.
[REI]
Last turn!
Haruka's caught up!
Makoto started strong,
but he's losing speed.
What did I say?
[MAKOTO panting]
[gasps]
[applause]
[MAKOTO gasps]
[MAKOTO, HARU pant]
[MAKOTO panting]
You okay?
I lost!
Congratulations.
Between the two of us,
you're still the
best in the water.
How awesome is that?
[sighs]
[HARUKA]
You're so weird.
[ANNOUNCER 6A] Next up,
the men's 100-meter freestyle.
[GOU]
This is what we're here for.
Haru versus Rin.
[whistle blowing]
[REFEREE 6A]
Ready.
--[beep]
--[CROWD] Go!
[SASABE] Let's go! Let's go!
Let's go! Let's go!
Let's go, Haruka!
[IWATOBI CLUB] Let's go!
Let's go! Let's go! Let's go!
Let's go, Haruka!
Yeah! Fight!
[SAMEZUKA CLUB] Fight!
Fight! Fight! Fight! Fight!
Kill it, Rin. Come on.
[REI]
Unbelievable.
No one else even
touches those two.
It's insane.
[CROWD cheers]
And it's official,
Haruka's first place.
They were less than
a second apart!
Rin was behind him by .02.
Wow. That's incredible!
[AMAKATA] Well, that was
heart-stopping, wasn't it?
Nanase doesn't disappoint!
No joke! So conflicted.
[laughs]
[NAGISA]
Hey.
I'm not sure I understand.
Why'd you race Haru
in the 200 again?
Well, what can I say?
Sometimes you just have
to know how you measure up.
[MAKOTO]
Sometimes...
Like, maybe, when you're
not sure where you stand.
[NAGISA]
Gotcha.
[MAKOTO]
Haru, you were totally amazing.
After today, I bet
scouts from all over
the country'll have
their eyes on you.
So, uh, what are you gonna do
if one of 'em approaches you?
Given it any thought?
I'm not gonna "do" anything.
[MAKOTO]
What's that supposed to mean?
[HARUKA] It means that I don't
care about being scouted.
I swim 'cause I
want to. That's it.
What's wrong?
[MAKOTO] Uh-- Nothing. Guess
I'll see you in the morning.
[RIN] No matter who wins
today, no hard feelings.
Deal? Just make sure you
make it to Regionals.
[HARUKA]
Like I need you to remind me.
[laughs] I let you walk away
with the freestyle
race yesterday.
But today'll be
a different story.
I'm sure the boys'll
be okay out there.
[whistle blowing]
[REFEREE 7A]
On your marks. Get set.
--[beep]
--[CROWD] Go!
Oh, no! He got a late start!
[AMAKATA]
It's okay!
I think Makoto can
make up for it!
[MOMOTARO]
[IWASHIMIZU]
Looking good, Momo!
[UOZUMI]
You guys, he's taking the lead!
Yeah. Fight!
[SAMEZUKA CLUB]
Fight! Fight!
[SASABE]
Makoto is catching up to him!
Go! Nagisa!
His usual extension
on the return leg
doesn't seem to be working!
[GOU] Samezuka's maintaining
the lead after the exchange!
There's a chance Rei may
not be able to catch up!
Samezuka's just so fast!
Haru!
Swim, Haru!
[REI]
Guys, Rin is turning first!
[RIN]
Yeah!
[SAMEZUKA CLUB]
All right, all right, Samezuka!
We just lost.
But they made it
past the prelims.
Which means we move on to
the regional tournament!
Good job.
[MOMOTARO]
Hey-hey, we got first place!
[RIN]
Yeah!
Way to go! Woo!
[NAGISA] They made a real
banner for us this time.
[MAKOTO] Last year they
reused the one they had
for the Judo Club, remember?
[NAGISA] Yeah. So can
anyone tell me why
I don't feel very
happy right now?
Is that a rhetorical question?
It's because we lost
to Samezuka, obviously!
Oh, come on, people,
you're telling me
that doesn't chap your
hide the tiniest bit?
I'm ecstatic we
advanced and all.
But victory tastes bitter when
one must share it with a rival.
We were made fools of.
I've never been so
humiliated in my life.
[HARUKA]
Then how 'bout we practice?
[REI, NAGISA, MAKOTO]
Okay!
[GOU]
You guys, look at this!
Makoto, Rei and Nagisa
all advanced to Regionals,
but your times in the
individual competitions
were barely fast enough
to make the cut.
See, I've got the
numbers right here!
All the top spots are filled
with Samezuka swimmers!
[MAKOTO] Well, I suppose
our times can't stand up
against Samezuka
Academy after all.
[GOU] The only one who
managed to stay at the top
of his category was
Haru in freestyle.
The long and short
of it is this:
Iwatobi is a long way from
being able to compete.
Here's the deal.
We can't be satisfied with
mediocre results like this.
We've gotta work
harder than ever--
[AMAKATA]
Big news, everyone! Big news!
[MAKOTO]
Miss A? What's the matter?
I just now got a call
from a talent scout
who's interested in
taking a look at Haruka!
[REI, NAGISA, MAKOTO gasp]
[AMAKATA]
They said they saw you
in the 100-meter freestyle
race two days ago.
Yeah, that's great news.
Wow, Haru, you did it!
Well, I suppose this
gives you an answer
about what to do
after graduation.
There's an old saying
that applies here.
"Tomorrow will take care of
itself if you give it a chance.
And the choices you make
today will help define
the future of your tomorrows"...
[splash]
[MAKOTO]
Haru.
I wonder what Haru wants
to do after graduation.
Well, I'm not exactly sure.
But I know he wrote "Free"
on his career-planning thing.
"Free"? What is that
supposed to mean?
Uh. He can't possibly
mean "freeter," can he?
Probably not, no.
Hey, maybe he means
"freelance competitive swimmer?"
Yeah, I don't think
it's that either.
Then what does it mean?
Could be anything, really.
Maybe at the end of the day,
in Haru's mind, "free"
just means "free."
Great, now I'm really confused.
[sighs] Although, that would
be in character for the man.
[AMAKATA] There was another
great offer from a scout today.
But Haruka doesn't
seem to care one bit.
Apparently, they
were beating down
my brother's door, too!
I wouldn't worry about
Haru that much,
he's in a great position.
He's got lots of options.
He'll figure something out.
I wonder if that's
what he really wants.
[GOU]
Huh?
[MAKOTO]
Oh, nothing.
Speaking of which,
have you decided
what you're gonna
do after graduation?
Well, uh...
To tell you the truth,
I don't know yet.
I might go to community college.
Wow, that surprises me.
[NAGISA]
Wow, Mako, you got "best luck!"
Oh, that's super good!
"You will win multiple contests!
A thousand blessings
follow you there!
Your lucky directions
are north and east!"
I just want you to know,
whatever anyone else says,
I think your
swimming is sublime.
[REI] I don't base that
on theory or calculations
or anything of the sort.
There's simply a power in it,
one that inspires
me to outdo myself.
It's freedom.
Rei.
[REI] No matter what happens,
as long as you're free,
you'll be happy till
the end of your days.
True, the word has
multiple meanings.
But to me, really being
free means not being
held captive by
anyone or anything.
It means possessing
a free spirit
and truly following your heart.
That's why it doesn't
matter what you choose.
As long as Haruka stays true
to Haruka, all else is a vapor.
Freedom is being yourself.
[REI]
Oh, dear. How awkward.
Who am I to tell you
all this, right?
[NAGISA]
You made this training regimen?
[HARUKA] Well, I modified
Gou's a little bit.
What? This is incredible.
You added practice
for relay exchanges.
This is rather
exceptionally clever--
we can drill those
hand-offs over and over.
If we cut down on our
exchange time enough,
winning Regionals is
a genuine possibility!
[HARUKA]
That's right.
[REI] If we stick to this plan
and work together as a team,
we can definitely close the
gap between us and Samezuka!
It's important to me
that you all know
what I want right now.
And more than anything else,
I wanna swim with you guys.
We feel the same way, Haru!
So let's make it happen!
Let's work our tails off!
Let's swim, till Rin and
his brood concede victory!
I'm in.
[STAFF]
How are you this evening?
[MAKOTO]
Can't complain.
All right.
Coach Sasabe! Hey!
Well! If it isn't ol' Makoto!
[MAKOTO]
Jeez, it looks like things
are pretty busy here tonight.
Yeah.
We're hoppin', all right,
which is great and all,
just sorta hard on
a skeleton crew.
I'm sorry I haven't been able
to watch your practices.
It's been crazy.
Wow.
Oh, I've got a little
somethin' for you.
Here, Gou wanted me to pass off
the final numbers from District.
[GIRL 8C] Coach Sasabe,
hurry up! We're waiting!
[SASABE]
Ah! Right!
Have no fear, I'm on my way!
Hey, Coach, wait!
[SASABE]
Huh?
Uh, I could maybe
give you a hand.
What? Are you serious?
'Course. Unless I'd
just be in the way.
[NAGISA]
What?
So you're working as an
assistant for Coach Sasabe
and teaching kids
how to dog paddle?
[MAKOTO]
Coach has done so much for us.
I thought it might be nice
to return the favor, you know?
He can use the help.
I think that we should
work together as a team
to get ISCR out of the weeds!
We've got your back,
Mako! Am I right?
I mean, you'll help us,
too, won't you, Rei?
Oh, definitely!
That's really nice.
I appreciate it.
Except, don't you guys,
have better things to do
than watch a bunch
of kids tread water?
Yeah, but--!
What about you, Haru?
Don't you think we ought
to be there to help him out?
All I care about is swimming.
Makoto can do whatever he wants.
Haru!
Okay, well.
[KIDS]
Okay, we're ready when you are!
Just always remember
to do your best!
I have a question.
What are we gonna
be working on today?
I thought we'd start things off
with a little kicking practice.
How does that sound?
[KIDS]
Awesome!
[KIDS chattering]
Bye, Coach! I'll
see you tomorrow!
Bye. This was fun!
'Kay, see ya next time!
[GIRL 8B]
Bye, bye!
[MAKOTO]
Hayato.
Hey. You okay?
What's wrong? You seem upset.
It's swimming. I hate it.
[gasps]
[KISUMI]
Hayato!
[HAYATO]
Big brother!
Really sorry I'm late, buddy!
That's Kisumi.
[MAKOTO]
Kisumi! What's up?
Makoto? Hey, man!
This is nuts. I haven't
seen you in forever!
Yeah, it's been a while.
I guess we haven't seen
each other since junior high.
[MAKOTO] Hayato told me
that he hates swimming.
Any idea what that's about?
If I knew why, it might
help me reach him.
Truth is, it's
probably my fault.
[MAKOTO]
Huh?
[KISUMI]
A while back...
We were out on
a boat in the ocean
with the rest of the family.
Hayato got to screwin'
around on the deck,
and he fell overboard.
[KISUMI] We're lucky they
got to him as quickly
as they did or, well...
Poor kid.
Whole thing must have
been terrifying for him.
That does sound really scary.
[KISUMI]
Ever since the incident,
he's hated his swimming
class at school.
And if I'd been better
about watching him
on that stupid boat, none
of this would've happened.
He wouldn't be afraid.
Kisumi...
[KISUMI] But, as much as
I want him to get past it--
[MAKOTO]
Wait.
If it's cool, I wanna
help Hayato learn to swim.
You do?
You wanna hear
something kinda strange?
He reminds me a little of myself
when I was that age, ya know?
Look, neither of you
should give up just yet.
So please, let me try.
You really do love swimming
more than anything else,
don't you, Makoto?
All right.
I'm leaving Hayato's
future to you, my friend.
If there's anything I can
do to help along the way,
just say the word.
Thanks. I won't let you down.
[KISUMI]
Hm?
Oh! Hey there!
[KISUMI]
Whoa. Haru!
I haven't seen you
in forever, buddy!
Wow! Oh, man, it's like
junior high all over again.
We met right after Rin went
to study abroad, didn't we?
You always seemed
so down about that.
Anyway, how've you been?
Kisumi, you went to the
same elementary school
as Rin, didn't you?
Oh! Yeah! Sosuke
went there, too.
Makoto.
[MAKOTO]
Crap! Is it that late already?
Hey, let's go.
What's wrong, you
mad or somethin'?
It's been so long, I thought
you'd be glad to see me.
[sighs] Don't worry, I'm glad.
Heh! Way to sell it.
[HAYATO]
Hey, big brother!
[KISUMI]
Hayato!
Well, I gotta run, you guys.
But we should catch up
or somethin' sometime!
[sighs]
[MAKOTO]
Guess we better get going, too.
[MAKOTO] I'm afraid if I
give him too much advice,
I might confuse him
and make him more scared
to swim than he already is.
We were all scared of
swimming at one point.
Think about what
you did to overcome
your fears and start there.
[MAKOTO]
Well, when I first started out,
I realized when I
swam the backstroke
I could see the sky.
And then I wasn't
scared anymore.
[MAKOTO] But, these days
they don't usually teach
backstroke until much later,
so that doesn't really help us.
[HARUKA] Yeah, but who
cares what "they" do?
Huh?
You're the teacher.
Do it how you wanna do it.
Yeah?
You know, you're right.
I might just give it a try.
[MAKOTO]
Hayato.
I've got an idea.
How 'bout we try
a different style of swimming?
It's one where you
don't have to put
your face in the water.
You know, you can even look
at the sky while you swim.
That sounds cool.
But there's no way
I could do that.
I promise to hold you
up the whole time,
so don't worry.
No matter what happens,
I won't let you sink.
I can't do it. Because--
'Cause I'm... scared!
[MAKOTO] It's okay. I won't
let go, you have my word.
Trust me.
But isn't it... scary?
Only till it's not.
[GIRL 8B]
We believe in you!
[GIRL 8A]
You can do it!
Let's go.
All you have to do is kick
your legs in the water
to move forward. You got this!
[MAKOTO]
Okay, now slowly open your eyes.
[gasps]
[laughs]
Wow! The backstroke?
High five!
[HAYATO]
Thanks!
[KISUMI]
Hayato!
[laughs]
[KIDS]
Way to go, Hayato!
[KIDS chattering, laughing]
[MAKOTO]
Hayato?
So, I uh...
Well, I want you to know...
I'm not afraid anymore!
It was really fun!
That's because you worked
so hard out there.
[gasps] Wow. Thank you.
This was amazing, Coach!
[MAKOTO chuckles]
[MAKOTO]
Good work today!
[STAFF]
Yeah, you, too!
Hey, Makoto, hold up a sec!
I wanted to let you know I
hired a new part-timer today,
so we won't need ya anymore.
You're off the hook.
It'll be a week
before he starts,
so I can use you till then.
What's wrong? I thought
you would be thrilled.
Uh...
Oh, yeah.
Well, thanks for the help
and be safe goin' home.
[MAKOTO]
Right. Thanks, Coach.
[AMAKATA]
You're still practicing?
My goodness, it's so late.
[MAKOTO]
Yeah, but--
[AMAKATA]
It's way past closing time.
The guidance counselor
is going to blow a gasket
if he sees you boys
here at this hour.
We're comin' up on the last
week before Regionals.
We gotta squeeze in all
the practice we can.
Our times are good,
but the exchanges
need tweaking if we
expect to have a shot.
Whaddya say we
give it another go?
Sure.
[AMAKATA]
Exchanges?
[MAKOTO]
Right.
Those milliseconds
between one guy touching
the platform and the
next one divin' in.
Tightening up that trade-off
moment is what separates
the men from the boys.
[MAKOTO] The idea is to predict
your partner's end time.
If you can anticipate the
moment he's gonna touch
the platform without
havin' to watch him,
you can tweak your dive stance
to get the most
out of your entry.
We're trying to shave our
exchange times down to zero.
Isn't that cutting
it awfully close?
I mean, what happens
if you hit the water
before the other's
reached the wall?
Instant disqualification.
It's just one of the
risks you learn to accept
for the sake of the team.
Miss A, we know it's
late, but mastering
this technique is
gonna give us an edge
against the competition.
[PRINCIPAL 9A]
Practice is running long, I see.
[MAKOTO]
Oh. Hello, sir.
[AMAKATA]
Oh, no, it's the principal!
I'm dreadfully sorry, sir!
I just told these boys it's
well past time to wrap up!
[COUNSELOR 9A]
Ah, you're fine. No harm done.
[PRINCIPAL 9A]
Stay as long as you need.
It's not often one our own
gets scouted by the pros.
Eh, Nanase?
We haven't been this
excited about Regionals
in quite some time.
Every member of the faculty
is as thrilled as can be.
Do your school proud.
Yes, sir.
[NAGISA]
This place is huge!
Wow. Quite an upgrade from
where we stayed last year.
[MAKOTO] Watch us get
stuck in a broom closet
while Miss A and Gou
get a tricked out
presidential suite or somethin'.
[REI] I do not need a flashback
to training camp right now.
Please, it's not the same thing.
That's right.
You gentlemen are the
stars of this show,
so you get star treatment.
Before you go nuts,
remember the old proverb:
"Nothing in this world
is more expensive
than that which comes free,
for it is invaluable!"
[GOU]
Okay, fellahs! It's chow time!
Miss Amakata gave us enough
cash to feed a small army,
so pick whatever looks good!
Does it have to be healthy?
[HARUKA]
This is my pick.
[NAGISA]
Cool!
Naturally.
Of course.
[MIKOSHIBA laughs]
That's a pretty good one,
[GOU]
Is that who I think it is?
[REI]
What's he doing here?
Hey!
Gou, sweetheart, we gotta
stop meetin' like this.
[NAGISA, REI, GOU]
Hey, Mikoshiba.
And who might this be?
Ah!
Lemme introduce you to Todou,
my university's top scout!
Seriously?
[MIKOSHIBA] I figured I'd show
him what the Samezuka team's
capable of.
These guys are competing
this weekend, too.
Is that by chance
Nanase from Iwatobi?
You bet!
Wait a second, this man's
actually heard of Haru?
[TODOU]
In my line of work, who hasn't?
Hi there. Honor to
meet you, young man.
You've got quite the reputation.
After that District
tournament, your freestyle
has become something
of a minor legend.
You've been on my
radar for a while.
Mine and every college
with a swim team.
Not to sound preachy,
but are you even aware
of how much potential
you have, son?
Can't let that
talent go to waste.
Stay focused and the sky's
the limit, I assure you.
You'll have lots of eyes
on you in tomorrow's race.
[laughs]
So how long's he
been gone, exactly?
I dunno, he snuck off
while I was in the shower.
You know him, he's probably
out joggin' or whatever.
[RIN]
Great.
The entire place is crawling
with college scouts.
Of all nights to go MIA.
That guy is such a loose cannon.
So, d'you wanna talk to him
about somethin', or...?
[RIN] Yeah, I wanna
ask him if he's decided
what he wants to do yet.
Guess he's just
running away, as usual.
Big shock there.
What is he thinking?
[MAKOTO] I wouldn't
read too much into it.
With some people, it's just
how they clear their heads.
He's more of a doer
than a talker.
Well, that's a polite
way of puttin' it.
[laughs]
Okay. Enough about him.
What's the story with you?
Uh?
Look, there's no reason
a swimmer at your level
wouldn't be scouted by at
least a second-tier school.
[MAKOTO]
Well...
[knocking]
[NAGISA]
Hey, guys, you've seriously
gotta check this out--
[REI, NAGISA]
Rin?
Do none of you people even care
that we're swimming
Regionals tomorrow?
Go to bed!
[NAGISA]
Ow!
Cut us some slack,
it's barely 11.
[REI]
Is everything all right, or...?
I just dropped by to talk
to Haru for a minute.
But, I mean, he's
out doing whatever,
so I guess I'll have
to wait. Goodnight.
[NAGISA]
Hey, hold up.
Tomorrow, you're goin' down.
Now that's the
attitude I wanna see.
[PRINCIPAL 9A]
Every member of the faculty
is as thrilled as can be!
Do your school proud.
[TODOU] You'll have lots of eyes
on you in tomorrow's race.
[CROWD cheering]
[HARUKA]
I can't see.
The big moment's finally here.
What are you talking about?
This is what we trained for!
The best part is,
there's no telling how many
scouts'll be watching
us out there!
[HARUKA]
Good for them.
[REI] Theoretically speaking,
given the waves you've made
at District, it's a
well-nigh impossibility
to slip under their radar.
You've got this!
I get it. Stop.
Your swimming is just
wonderful, Nanase.
[HARUKA panting]
[AMAKATA] There's an old
saying that's appropriate.
"You may run all you like,
but in the end,
your problems will always
know where to find you."
[GOU]
Haruka.
My brother's really looking
forward to this match.
[RIN]
What are you waitin' for?
It's now or never.
[CROWD cheering]
[HARUKA panting]
[REFEREE 9A]
On your marks!
[TODOU]
That's it, kid.
We're all here for you.
Give us the goods!
Show us freedom!
[HARUKA gasps]
[pants]
This is gonna be so cool!
Yes, well, and nerve wracking.
You okay, Haru? Hey.
It's nothing. I'm fine.
[SWIMMER 9A]
Check it out! University scouts.
All over the place.
How do you spell that?
I'm not sure.
[SWIMMER 9B]
There's a ton of 'em, huh?
[GUY 9C]
No kidding.
[SWIMMER 9D]
We need to look sharp out there.
We want the big schools
fallin' all over themselves
to recruit us, right?
[MAKOTO]
Haru?
Hey. Earth to Haru.
[gasps] Huh?
Are you sure you're all right?
Uh... Stop asking me.
I told you, I'm good.
It's just about that time.
Let's win this thing!
Good luck, you guys!
Go kick some butt!
[REI, NAGISA]
Yeah!
Okay. I guess this is
the moment of truth.
So let's give it our best.
[REI, NAGISA]
Right!
[ANNOUNCER 9A]
Men's 100-meter backstroke,
third heat, begins now!
--[REI] Go for it, Makoto!
--[GOU] Give 'em hell, Makoto!
It's all you, come on!
[whistle blowing]
[REFEREE 9A]
Ready.
--[beep]
--[CROWD] Go!
[GOU] Let's go, let's go, let's
go, let's go, let's go Makoto!
[IWATOBI CLUB]
Let's go, let's go, let's go,
let's go, let's go, Makoto!
[GOU]
Push it, push it, push it,
push it, push it, Makoto!
[IWATOBI CLUB]
Push it, push it, push it,
push it, push it, Makoto!
--[REI] You got this!
--[NAGISA] Go, Mako!
[GOU]
Last lap, go!
[IWATOBI CLUB]
Last lap, go! Last lap, go!
[GOU]
Last lap, go!
[IWATOBI CLUB]
Last lap, go! Last lap, go!
Yeah!
This is a totally
different animal
than District, evidently.
[NAGISA]
You can say that again.
[RIN] Sucks Makoto didn't
make it to the finals,
I thought he had a shot.
[HARUKA]
Yeah.
[RIN]
So, have you made a decision?
[HARUKA]
Not really.
What the hell's your problem?
You saw how many top tier scouts
came out of the
woodwork after District.
I couldn't get a moment's peace.
If they came for me,
they came for you.
Whatever. I'll hit you up
on this again after the race.
Good luck out there.
[ANNOUNCER 9A] Next, we have
the men's 100-meter freestyle,
sixth heat.
I have a feeling
Haru's gonna wow us.
[gasps]
[whistle blows]
[REFEREE 9A]
Ready.
--[beep]
--[CROWD] Go!
[HARUKA panting]
[HARUKA]
No.
What's happening?
What's he doing?
[footsteps]
[RIN]
Haru!
[RIN] What was that?
Are you outta your mind?
[HARUKA]
Like it's any of your business.
[RIN]
What?
Do you realize how many
scouts just saw you tank?
Why should I care about them?
[gasps]
[HARUKA]
Who are they to me?
What is any of this to me?
You think I do this for
the crowds, or so I can say
"Hey, look at my awesome time?"
Why do you do it, then?
I swim for myself.
And my friends.
Then you owe it to them
and yourself to give a care!
At least give 'em the
benefit of the doubt!
You have something here!
If you'd just take it seriously
for once in your life!
You think your friends
wanna stand there
and watch you piss
away your future?
[gasps]
No one asked you to
care about my future!
What "future"? What is
it you think I have?
This is my life, not yours!
I'm not you! I'm never
going to be you!
[MAKOTO]
Haru.
You didn't mean any of that.
How long have you guys
been standing there?
[HARUKA]
Listen. It's okay. We're a team.
And I'm still gonna swim relay.
I didn't come this far not to.
[REI] I couldn't make it
to the individual finals.
[NAGISA]
Neither could I.
You were really close though.
Seriously, you should
be proud of yourself.
No one would ever
believe that you've only
been swimming competitively
for like, barely over a year.
Thanks, I appreciate that.
But it wasn't just me.
Your time seemed like it
could make the finals, too.
I was very impressed
with your swimming.
Well, thank you
for saying so, Rei.
I feel like we can
win the relay.
So um, you think
Haruka will be all right?
Obviously!
He said he wanted
to swim with us.
He's not real big
on making things up.
Maybe we should just take
him at his word, yeah?
Yeah, maybe.
[TAKAMARU]
I can't swim the way I want.
It makes me so nervous...
[REI] If we're gonna do it, then
we might as well try to win.
[NAGISA]
Right?
[REI] We'll swim in a way
only the Iwatobi Team can.
--[NAGISA] Yeah!
--[ASAHI] ...training to me.
[TAKAMARU]
Mental training?
What type of stuff did you do?
[ASAHI laughs]
Talk to myself in the mirror.
[TAKAMARU]
C'mon, what'd you really do?
[NAGISA]
Rei? You good?
Uh-huh. Yeah, yeah, I'm fine.
[HANAMURA]
Congrats on getting to Nationals
for the medley relay!
Thank you so much!
I can't tell you
how inspired I am
by Hazuki and
Ryugazaki's hard work.
I know, right? And
of course we can't forget
about how incredible
Haruka and Makoto were!
So amazing. I mean,
at this rate,
they should have no
problem at Nationals.
Well, uh...
"Well, uh," what?
It's just that their relay time
should be getting better,
but ever since the
tournament, it hasn't been.
Do you think there's
something wrong with Nanase?
Huh?
[HANAMURA] That race did seem
a little off, don't you think?
[NAGISA] I wonder why
Haru keeps staying late
to practice by himself.
I don't really know.
I suppose there's
no chance he'll opt
to swim freestyle at Nationals.
Guess not.
Honestly, more than
anything else,
I just hope he's okay.
[NAGISA]
He'll be fine.
[REI]
Freestyle is everything to him.
It's part of who
he is as a person.
Seeing how awesome
he was at freestyle
inspired me to wanna
be great, too.
I thought, "If I could swim
like Haruka, I'd have it made!"
When we're at Nationals,
if he opts out
of the individual race,
he'll regret it.
[REI]
What if relay just isn't him?
What if he's only
doing it for our sakes?
What?
How can you think that Haru
loving the relay is a bad thing?
I don't understand--
are you saying
you don't wanna swim with him?
Of course I want to
swim with Haru--
it's the only thing I want!
Trouble is, I just want Haruka
to be the Haruka who's free.
The Haru who swims
because he loves it
more than anything in the world.
[NAGISA] Yeah, I know
exactly what you mean.
[MAKOTO]
Obon's nearly here.
[HARUKA]
Yeah.
[MAKOTO]
Will your parents be home soon?
[HARUKA]
Not till the end of summer.
[MAKOTO chuckles] They're free
spirits just like you.
Haru! Let's go to the
Fireworks Festival.
We can invite
Nagisa and Rei, too!
That sounds fun.
Well, bye.
Hey, wait!
I was thinking.
About what'll happen
when we graduate.
I don't really wanna
talk about that.
No! Uh... It's not
what you think!
[REN]
Big brother!
--[MAKOTO] Whoa!
--[REN] Hi!
Hope you're hungry,
'cause dinner's ready!
Hey, you should come eat, too!
Yeah, we have plenty of food!
Today's not a good day for me.
[RAN]
Aw!
[REN] You promise you'll
eat with us next time?
Deal.
[REN, RAN]
Good night, Haru.
[GOU]
Everybody pay attention.
I took the liberty
of creating a chart
that shows all of
your race times.
But according to this, our times
aren't really
improving that much.
Yes, I know.
These stats are after Regionals.
Individual times have
improved quite a bit.
But for some strange reason,
your relay times
have leveled off.
I don't understand.
How is that possible?
Does this mean we do worse
when we swim together?
[REI]
That can't be true!
[GOU] Whatever it means,
it's a problem.
To start with, Coach Sasabe
is going to adjust
your training regimen.
Let's hope we can pin point
the root of the problem
and deal with it before
Nationals next week.
[NAGISA]
Whoa! What is this?
Remember?
Haruka carved it out
of wood to get people
to join Swim Club last year.
Pretty impressive
craftsmanship, if you ask me.
I remember, I just can't
believe you kept it!
Yeah.
[NAGISA] I wonder if we'll get
any new members next year.
I don't think we'll have
to worry about it too much.
Now that we've made
it to Nationals,
everyone and their
grandmother'll wanna join.
We'll have to turn people away.
They'll be coming out
in droves, I guarantee it!
But, after Nationals,
Makoto and Haru
will be moving on.
It'll just be the
two of us for a bit.
[NAGISA]
I wonder what Haru is gonna do.
[REI]
Hey, Nagisa.
What do you want for Haru?
If you could choose his future,
what would you wish for?
Well, I imagine
the same as you.
I want him to be himself,
but more than anything,
happy with his choices.
I don't know.
It makes me sad to see
him struggle like this.
I feel the same way.
This is the last
tournament the four of us
will ever swim together.
I wanna be certain
Haruka's in a good place.
Maybe we should
say something to him.
We're his friends.
We have to let him
know how we feel.
[REI, NAGISA]
Wow.
My, this is beautiful.
Yep.
Hey, Haruka.
What is it?
There's something we need
to talk about as a team.
And we need to do it
now before we swim
in the National Tournament.
Because, if we don't,
then I don't think
we have a chance of winning.
[REI]
Haruka, listen.
You're an incredible swimmer.
Nagisa and I agree that
you're the best freestyler
we've ever seen.
But now that you're
not swimming freestyle,
something has changed,
and not for the better.
Simply put, you're
not yourself anymore.
Truth is, we just want you to
compete at the next level.
To swim in front of people
from all over the country.
'Cause the world should
know how amazing you are.
Don't you see?
You have the power
to inspire people
to pursue dreams of their own.
[REI] Make no mistake,
when the world sees talent,
it's moved. Exactly as
we were the first time
we watched you swim.
People all over will aspire
to reach your level.
Is there anything more
beautiful than inspiring others?
Haru, they've got a point.
I wish I could see
what you mean.
[NAGISA]
Will he be okay?
I sure hope so, Nagisa.
I thought I might find you here.
Haru. Listen to me.
You can't keep
goin' on like this.
Till now, I've always figured,
"if he says he's okay, then
that's the way things are."
I ignored what Rin said.
I wanted to be considerate
of you and your feelings.
But then, I overheard
something you said to him
in the locker room at Regionals.
[HARUKA] What "future?"
What is it you think I have?
This is my life, not yours!
I'm not you! I'm never
going to be you!
This is your life.
And if what you really want
is for me to stay out of it,
then I can do that.
All you have to do
is say the word.
But, if you're stuck
'cause you can't
find your dream,
that's different.
I only want you to know that
I'm here to help you find it.
You're here to
"help me find it?"
You can find it just by looking?
Is that how simple
a dream really is?
I don't know.
Thanks, but no.
Let's not talk
about this anymore.
[MAKOTO]
Hold on.
Let go of me!
Don't walk away!
Listen to me, Haru!
Why? It won't change anything!
A dream's not something
you stumble across.
I'm fine just the way I am!
That's a lie!
You wanna find your dream,
too, you're just afraid!
So stop bein' a coward, already!
All you have to do is go out
into the world and find it.
You have enough
talent to do that!
Why does everyone wanna talk
about my talent, huh?
Where I swim,
and who I swim for--
That is my business
and nobody else's!
I said I'm fine,
so just leave me alone!
Oh, come on, Haru,
that's a load of crap!
You're not fine and you know it,
That's why they're all worried!
Nagisa and Rei. Rin.
And me, too.
Why don't you understand
that we love you?
You're important to
every single one of us.
So why do you keep
pushing us all away?
Because we want you
to find your dream?
Because we want you to
have a successful future?
[HARUKA]
Tch!
You're one to talk
about having a future!
What does the future
have in store, Makoto?
[gasps]
You see? You don't know.
So, for the last time,
would you just leave me alone?
You got no right sayin'
these things to me
when you don't
even know yourself!
It just makes you a hypocrite.
[MAKOTO]
You're wrong.
Dead wrong.
I'm going to college in Tokyo.
[firework whistles]
[MAKOTO]
I've been meaning to tell you.
I just couldn't find the
right words, I suppose.
Listen...
I couldn't care less
what you do!
Haru!
[doorbell rings]
[ringing continues]
[HARUKA]
This had better be good.
Rin?
Haru, wake up.
We're goin' somewhere.
[HARUKA]
Uh...
[RIN] Don't just stand
there--get dressed.
We're gonna be late.
Wait a sec. Where are we going?
[RIN]
You might wanna pack a bag.
'Cause we're
headed to Australia.
[IMMIGRATION OFFICER 12A] What's
the reason for your visit?
What do I tell him?
We're sightseeing.
Slow down.
Yo! Feel like tellin'
me where we're going?
You wanna know, follow me.
Right now, we're getting
on a bus. Come on.
Wait, what the...? Ugh!
[NAGISA]
What? You're kidding!
Haru's gone all
the way to Australia?
I can't make heads
or tails of it.
I mean, seriously, what would
possess Rin to go back there?
[MAKOTO] I knew he was tryin'
to get through to him and all,
but Australia?
I guess I didn't realize
know how far Rin would go
to make his point.
What in the world does he
think he'll accomplish?
[MAKOTO]
Who knows?
I mean, your guess
is as good as mine.
But Rin's got
something up his sleeve,
and I think it might be
a wake-up call for Haru.
At least I hope so.
Yeah, I'm with you.
As long as he figures out
what makes him happy.
[BIRD calls]
[sighs]
[HARUKA]
Rin?
Rin? Where the--?
[RIN]
Over here.
Figured you may be
thirsty. You all right?
You can't run off
on me like that, Rin.
Sorry.
While we're at it,
I'm sorry for what I said.
You think your friends
wanna watch you
piss away your future?
No one asked you to
care about my future!
[RIN] I wasn't looking
at your side of things.
I was just puttin'
all my own crap on you.
[RIN]
So, yeah.
The thing is, there's
something I want you to know.
When it's all said and done,
you've always been
someone I looked up to.
[gasps]
[RIN]
Whew! That's a load off, huh?
Let's go.
Go where?
Cut me some slack.
Don't look so terrified.
Pretty sweet, right?
Great view to relax by.
Helps clear your head.
What do you say?
Sorry, I'm not
really feelin' it.
You're killin' me, Haru.
What happened to the freak
who would strip down
when he got within
20 feet of water?
Give it a rest.
Nobody forced you
to get on that plane.
You could've said no any time.
I didn't expect you to come.
What changed your mind?
[HARUKA]
Nothing.
I-I just don't wanna
be home right now.
You and Makoto had
a falling out, huh?
That's gotta suck.
No big. It happens.
Sosuke and I get
into it all the time.
[HARUKA]
Yeah, well.
It was our first fight.
Well, there's a silver lining.
Makoto finally settled on what
he's gonna do after graduation.
He wants to tell you all
about it once we're back.
Man, this is gorgeous.
Really puts it all into
perspective, ya know?
At least for me.
When I first came here,
back in the day,
if I got stressed out,
the ocean always calmed me down.
Oh-ho, Rin!
So how you been keepin'?
Things good back in Japan?
[RIN]
Things are great, Russell.
Good to see you!
I can't get over
how big you've gotten!
Well, I swim every day,
so, you know.
Every day? That's
some dedication!
[RIN chuckles]
Yep!
[RUSSELL] You and that old mate
of yours still lockin' horns?
[LORI]
Haruka, yeah? Was that his name?
Am I remembering it right?
--[RUSSELL] Oh, yeah. Haru.
--[LORI] Wait,
--is that him over there?
[RIN]
That's him.
C'mon, man!
Don't be rude. Say hello.
Haru, this is my
home-stay family.
Meet Russell and Lori!
[LORI] Help yourself. 'S not
rude to stuff your face here.
Thanks, it looks great.
Rin, your friend is just
as you described him.
Cool as a cucumber and eyes
that look like the ocean.
Don't embarrass him.
Chill out. Don't get a big head.
I was just trying to paint
a picture of home.
[RUSSELL] Rin tells us
your thing is freestyle.
That true?
Nothin' else do it for ya? Wow.
Yeah. Well, you know.
[HARUKA] Did you tell these
people my whole life story,
or what?
Uh, not really?
I don't know if you're aware
of this or not, Haru,
but by the way Rin
talked, I could tell
you're someone he
truly looks up to.
Can we change the topic, please?
Screw that. I wanna
know what you said.
Is it really that important?
Little bit, yeah.
Ugh. What do you want from me?
I told you this afternoon.
[RUSSELL] So, mate, got
a girlfriend back home?
[RIN]
Long story. Or not, actually.
[RUSSELL laughs]
I'll take that as a no.
It's all right,
I was late bloomer, too.
[LORI chuckles]
Remember that little girl...
[RIN] Oh, don't go there, Lori.
Please. No, no, no.
[RUSSELL laughs]
[RUSSELL] It's summer back home
for you right now, yeah?
[LORI]
Does it get very hot over there?
[RIN]
Ugh. It's like a blast furnace.
Well, mates. Take care.
Lori and I had a
great time seein' ya.
Be well. Come back and
visit whenever ya like.
I'll keep in touch, all right?
Hey, and enjoy the posh digs.
Thanks, guys.
This was really great.
Till next time!
Got something on your mind?
Do what? No. No I'm good.
[RIN]
Cool. Let's get checked in.
What?!
There had better be
a cot, damn it.
Uh, did we get screwed or
is this normal for Australia?
[RIN]
We got screwed! I blame you.
You and that stupid
girl-sounding name.
What about yours, "sweetheart"?
Huh? Shut your face!
Make me!
Shut up!
Your name confuses--
Ugh, you know what?
Never mind. I don't
have time for this crap.
I'm gonna talk
to the front desk.
Unbelievable.
[HARUKA] Would you stop.
Just go to sleep.
[groans] Good night, I guess.
[RIN]
Hey, Haru?
What I told Lori and Russell
back in the day was true.
You probably don't remember
the first time we met,
but to me, it might as well
have been yesterday.
It's that vivid.
[RIN] At that point in my life,
it never occurred to me
that someone could
be faster than I was.
[RIN]
I was pissed off at first, sure.
But then I thought, "Wow.
There's someone out there
who can teach me somethin'.
I wanna swim like this guy."
[RIN] That's why, when you're
not out there ahead of me
blazin' a trail,
I feel kinda lost,
like I can't get my bearings.
It's 'cause of you that
I found out who I really was.
[HARUKA] I do remember.
That's was a crazy tournament.
What about that
last freestyle race?
Back in the spring?
Felt pretty good settin'
a new record together.
Sure.
[RIN] Don't take this the wrong
way, but I was testing you.
Felt like I had to.
I needed to see how
far you could go.
[RIN] Man, when I felt
you closin' the gap
between us, I knew.
There was no doubt in my mind.
You were in the
same league as me.
Post graduation, the world
would be our oyster.
C'mon. You can't tell me
you didn't feel it, too.
The future was wide open.
[RIN] I know you think all
your dreams are basically
somebody else's.
But here's the question:
what makes a dream really
and truly yours?
Well, here we are.
[HARUKA]
What is this?
[RIN] A place that separates
the men from the boys.
Let's do it.
[RIN]
Yo. Over here.
Take it in.
This is where the best
swimmers in the world
test their metal
against each other.
This is what I flew you
all the way here to see.
[RIN]
Well, not just see.
It's cool for us to swim?
As long as you got the heart.
It's anybody's lap pool.
Um, I didn't bring a swimsuit.
I got ya covered. Come on.
[RIN]
Hey, it's the National Team!
[HARUKA]
No kidding?
[RIN] Yeah, this is
where they practice.
You really sure it's okay
for us to be here?
I... I mean, no one
else is in the pool.
Well, there's this one and
the practice pool over there.
No problem usin' it if you
don't feel comfortable
swimmin' next to
the National Team.
Your call, mate.
[footsteps]
Hey. Hello.
[SWIMMER 12B]
Wanna race? Then let's go!
[CROWD cheering]
[HARUKA gasps]
[HARUKA]
This is it.
This is what I want.
Right here.
[HARUKA]
This is my dream.
[RIN]
Hey.
You wanna watch
or you wanna swim?
[HARUKA]
Swim.
[MAKOTO]
Haru! Rin!
[RIN]
Hey, Makoto!
Long way to come just
to see us get off the plane.
Bet you guys are pretty
wiped out from the trip.
Uh... Ah-- Uh...
[MAKOTO]
Haru.
It's good to see you.
[gasps]
Good to see you, too.
So, uh... What do ya
say we get goin'?
So, ya think we're
finally gettin'
our heads around
this pool, or what?
Yeah.
And just imagine two days
from now when these stands
will be filled with spectators!
Sounds like someone's
gettin' nervous.
Oh, please.
No, it just happens to be a day
we've all worked very hard for.
I'm as far from nervous
as it's possible to be!
Ah! So you've finally grown
some hair on your chest!
No, but what does that
have to do with anything?
Uh-- Makoto will be back
with them any minute now.
[NAGISA] Whoa. Guess we
lost track of time.
C'mon, Rei.
I can't help but wonder.
Do you really think the trip
had a positive effect on Haru?
[NAGISA]
Sure it did!
He just needed a little change
of scenery, that's all.
You'll see!
[REI]
Right!
Guys are here.
Thought it'd be good to
get to know the space.
You know, since
tomorrow's the big day.
Well, I'm gonna go meet
up with my team, so...
See ya 'round.
[HARUKA]
Rin!
Thanks a lot, man.
Sure.
[MAKOTO]
Hey!
[NAGISA]
Haru!
Welcome back!
Hi, Rei. Nagisa.
Hope the trip was cool!
Glad you made it home!
And, more importantly,
that you made it home safe.
[NAGISA]
You're such a mother hen, Rei.
He was super stressed out
about you the whole time.
[REI]
Shut up!
I'm sorry I made you
guys worry about me.
No biggie.
Just do us all a favor
and get plenty of rest
before the big tournament.
It is only two days away.
Of course, we still need to
make a few minor adjustments.
[NAGISA]
That's true.
[HARUKA]
Makoto.
Nagisa, Rei.
We need to talk. It's important.
[HARUKA] Till now, I was
never really concerned
about winning or
losing, you know?
I just swam 'cause I wanted to.
I thought if I made it
about tweaking my speed,
or beating the other team or
whatever, what'd be the point?
Rin wants to swim at
the international level.
He's diving into that world
head first after we graduate.
But, that's his thing.
Should I follow his
example if I just wanna
keep swimming, or is
that a compromise?
Is it for me to care
about winning?
I don't think so. I'm not Rin.
I don't have the
competitive streak he does.
[HARUKA]
So, that's why I couldn't answer
when you asked what my plan was.
I didn't have a clue.
Didn't think a dream was
something you could just grab.
But then, Rin took
me to Australia,
showed me all
this amazing stuff.
And suddenly,
it was like, I dunno.
[RIN] What makes a dream
really and truly yours?
[HARUKA] I felt it, like
the world got a lot bigger.
And me? I'd found
my place in it.
I wanna swim for
the rest of my life.
And if that means I gotta
start caring about times
and tournaments and all the
things that come with it,
that's fine with me.
Wow, that's quite a
change of heart for you.
It sounds like the trip with
Rin was a real eye opener.
I knew it was gonna work out!
If you've found your path,
then far be it from us
to give you anything
but support.
You better believe we'll be
cheering you on all the way!
I know you will.
[MAKOTO]
We're here. Do you believe it?
It still feels like a dream.
Makoto, I--
[HARUKA] The other day, I said
some really stupid things.
I didn't mean any of 'em.
I'm sorry.
[gasps] Haru.
If anybody's sorry, it's me.
We've been through a lot.
I oughta be able
to talk to my friend.
Seriously.
I should've told you what
my plans were before I did.
Truth is, competition
isn't my thing.
I'd been thinking about
just fallin' back
on community college
or somethin'.
Didn't know how to bring it up.
Sucks when you don't know what
you wanna do with your life.
Then Coach Sasabe
gave me that job
coaching little
kids at the club.
It was nothing special at first,
just helpin' him out and stuff.
I figured it was the least I
could do to repay him, ya know?
Then the kids
changed all of that.
I met Hayato,
and for some reason,
I really wanted to help
him learn to swim.
I was clueless at first.
But your advice actually made
more difference than you think.
Not like it was that profound.
[MAKOTO chuckles]
[MAKOTO] Well, the kid learned
how to do the backstroke.
And the look on his
face when he did--
I'd never seen anything
like it before in my life.
He was so proud of himself.
From that moment, I was hooked.
That's when I knew I
wanted to help kids feel
a sense of accomplishment,
take pride in themselves.
[MAKOTO]
I was put on this earth to bring
first timers to the water.
After graduation, I'm gonna
go to college in Tokyo
to make it happen.
That's my dream.
That's what I'm reaching for.
Not bad.
You do realize you're gonna
be awesome at it, right?
You really think so?
Thanks. It'll be the hardest
thing I've ever done.
[HARUKA]
Ha. No kidding.
[MAKOTO laughs]
[MAKOTO] I feel like we're
gonna see something today
that'll stay with us forever.
[HARUKA]
Definitely. All four of us.
[REI]
Agreed.
[NAGISA]
Let's do this!
[CROWD cheering]
[MAKOTO, REI, NAGISA gasp]
[ANNOUNCER 13A]
The first heat of the men's
400-meter medley
relay begins now.
Swimmers, on your marks.
[whistle blowing]
[SASABE]
Makoto!
[GIRLS]
[REFEREE 13A]
Ready.
--[beep]
--[CROWD] Go!
I remember this.
[laughs]
Nagisa!
[NAGISA laughs]
Go, Rei!
[gasps]
Go, Haruka!
[MAKOTO]
Haru.
[NAGISA]
Nice job.
[REI]
Beautifully done.
--[NAGISA] Haru!
--[MAKOTO] Come on!
--[GOU] Go, Haruka!
--[SASABE] Go, go!
[gasps]
[CROWD cheers]
[GOU]
He did it! He did it!
Heh.
[sobs]
[NAGISA, REI sobbing]
[laughing]
[sobbing]
[laughs]
[NAGISA]
It's over.
Hope you guys had as much
fun today as I did.
I did, for sure!
I have to admit I'm rather
proud of myself, too.
I've just swum a relay with
incredibly talented people.
Thank you all for
swimming with me.
Welcome, and thank you, as well.
So, um, do you think this
is really the end for us?
Come on, Nagisa,
don't look so sad.
It's not the end.
We've still got plenty of
time before graduation.
Oh, yeah, that's true.
[HARUKA]
Nagisa.
I'm glad you asked Makoto
and me to join Swim Club.
So, um. Thank you.
[laughs]
And, Rei, you should
be proud of yourself
for how far you've come.
Thank you, Haruka.
Also, even though this is over,
I know that we'll
always be friends.
I'll be counting on you
from now on, too.
Okay.
[HARUKA]
Makoto.
You've always been such
great support for us,
and it's been appreciated.
You're welcome, Haru.
[MAKOTO chuckles]
[BOTH laugh]
[ALL laugh]
[ALL]
Thank you, everyone!
Hey, you guys, check out
the clouds right now!
[MAKOTO]
Wow!
They look like wings!
That's so cool!
[laughs]
[REI]
It's beautiful.
[NAGISA] You know what? We need
to take a picture together!
[REI]
Nagisa, slow down!
Running like that
is very dangerous!
[NAGISA]
Don't be such a baby. Come on!
[MAKOTO]
Okay. Haru, you ready?
[SOSUKE]
Great, where am I?
[RIN]
Hey, where'd Sosuke run off to?
[UOZUMI] He went to get
something not too long ago.
Let me take a wild guess
and assume he got lost again?
Don't worry, sir.
I'll go look for him!
--[GIRL B] Come on!
--[BOY B] Go, Ikuya!
--Move it! Go!
You can do it, Kirishima!
[BOY A]
Go, Ikuya!
[SOSUKE]
Whoa. What's he doing here?
[NATSUYA]
Really? Good job.
How was your time? Think
you're hitting a plateau?
[IKUYA]
No. I'm good.
Really good, in fact.
My strokes have been
lengthening, too.
It's almost scary how little
I feel like I'm plateauing.
[NATSUYA laughs]
That's what I like to hear.
But Kinjo from
Suda-East and Terashima
from Oomori Academy are also
getting faster, aren't they?
Wasn't it a tough race?
[IKUYA]
I appreciate your concern.
However, I'm not
gonna lose to anyone.
[RIN]
Hey, Sosuke, I got a question.
Do you remember
that summer we met
and raced against each other?
[SOSUKE] I couldn't forget
it if I wanted to.
You know our match from
that day isn't over, Rin.
[RIN] Looks like this
summer's gonna be hot.
[SOSUKE] Yeah, let's make
it a really hot one.
[RIN] Next time: Free!
Timeless Medley: The Promise .
[SOSUKE] The seasons change,
and so do our feelings.
[RIN] It's still way too soon to
get to the finish line, Sosuke.