[BALMUNG] Move that tree a
little more to the right.
It's difficult to see
the tree behind it.
[WORKER] Yes, sir.
Well done.
That's very good.
Please continue.
[WORKER] Thank you, sir.
Reki?
[REKI] Yes, sir.
I was looking into
your encounter
with the Super Shogun
the other day, Lord Balmung...
[REKI] There was no record of it
in the system management log.
An Armored Super Shogun
has never appeared in that area.
[BALMUNG] Is that so?
[BALMUNG] So then,
what was it I fought?
Uh, Lord Balmung?
[BALMUNG] Please continue
with the investigation.
The personnel in
system management
are professionals
at managing data.
[REKI] Yes, sir.
Hmph. This event is
shaping up very nicely.
It'll be amongst
the best I've had
a hand in creating
in a long time.
Yeah, you say that
every time, sir...
Huh? Lord Balmung.
[SHUGO] Huh? You're back?
[FATHER] Yeah. I was on the
road and just stopped by.
I have to go back
to the office now.
I don't know if
I'll be home tonight.
Just do what you
want for dinner.
Oh...
[FATHER] Okay then.
'kay! Let's get going.
[SHUGO] Where is she...?
Hi Shugo!
Sorry to keep you wait--
You're late!
Ah! I-I said I'm sorry.
I wasn't THAT late... Hmm? Huh?
Aren't you that hunter...
The Rare Hunter of Love and
Courage, Mireille, remember?!
Hey, hey, where
are you going today?
Can I come with you?
Can I? Can I? Please?
We haven't decided where...
Then I shall be
your trusted guide.
[RENA] C'mon Shugo!
We are so outta here!
Speed Charm!
HEEEY!
[RENA] Buh-bye.
It's not very nice to
use that charm here!
As it turns out I've been
burned pretty badly before.
Oh, my goodness.
You've been burned?
I'm so sorry to hear that.
No, uh, that's not really
what I meant to say...
Hm... How can I say
it more clearly...?
Please, just say
whatever you'd like.
Looks like we've lost her.
Y'know I wouldn't
actually mind going
on an adventure
with that Rare Hunter.
I want to explore The World
with you, Shugo, not with her.
That's why we're here.
[SHUGO] Ah... Rena...
Hey... What's that?
[RENA] It's an event notice.
Whenever there is an event,
that's how it's advertised.
[SHUGO] Wow! I had no idea.
This one's for a
flower-viewing event
You can read that?
Well of course!
"Heroes, gather at the area,
Voluptuous Cherry Maze!
I look forward to the
blooming of glorious blossoms."
So, that actually
means something?
In other words, we need to go
to the area that it mentions,
then we need to figure out
how to make the flowers bloom.
If you can successfully
clear the event,
then you get some rare item
to add to your inventory.
Hey! Sounds like fun!
Wanna go?
Can anyone enter an event?
Oh, of course!
We'll use the gate to go to
Voluptuous Cherry Maze... Ah...
Is something wrong?
[RENA] It says here:
"Various skills are
required to clear this event."
Shugo, It might be difficult
for us to clear this event
without a Wavemaster
in our party.
A Wavemaster?
Guess what?
I'm a Wavemaster.
Maybe we can join forces and
clear out this event together?
Lucky us!!
Uh... This area is
Voluptuous Cherry Maze?
[MIREILLE] I don't get it.
They're not blooming at all!
[RENA] This is an event
to make them bloom!
Cherry blossoms... Oh...
Might as well
get started. Repth!
Nothing happened.
Did I miss something?
Uh...
Try this one... Pha Repth!
It doesn't look like recovery
spells are the answer here.
I got it, you
have to give water
to flowers to make
them bloom, right?
Water, yeah!
Yeah!
Rue Rom!
I guess that
wasn't it either...
[RENA] Hang on a second!
Try something that doesn't
get us all soaking wet.
Ah! Maybe what we need
is some kind of item
to help us out here.
I'll just go look for one!
Hey! Come baaaack!
Oh, man.
Now my costume's gotten
all soaked and ruined.
Breathtaking
like the dew drops
on a spring morning, isn't she?
Takes your breath
away, for sure.
Uh, what's that?
Uh, I didn't say anything.
There's nothing like
it to quench the thirst.
What is still lacking...
the flowers... yes.
[REKI] Lord Balmung...
Hey, what are you doing
hanging out here at this hour,
when today's event
has already started...
[REKI] Oh, ah...
you wrote code for sake?
You can't feel it's
effects here, you know?
Don't say that.
This is "refined."
Yeah, yeah.
And obviously it's
impossible for me
to have a sense of "refinement."
[BALMUNG]
So, about that monster...
[REKI] It's still
undergoing investigation.
Given who it is
we're dealing with...
This one's going
to take me some time.
[REKI] It seems that no one
has solved the event yet...
[BALMUNG] The landscape
remains dismal...
The beautiful sake sheds tears.
[REKI] Perhaps the
event was too difficult?
It's all common sense.
The heroes have returned...
Cherry blossoms...
When we were young,
we used to go see them a lot.
[children laughing]
[MOTHER] Shugo! Rena! Let's eat!
[FATHER] Or we'll eat it first.
[MOTHER]
Come on you two!
[YOUNG RENA] We won't let you!
Those were
some good times...
[SHUGO] Sometimes I wonder...
I wonder if fallen cherry
blossoms can be brought back?
[RENA] Shugo,
we need to figure out
a way to make those flowers
bloom, don't you think.
Huh? Yeah.
[dog barks]
[SHUGO] Hey, Rena!
It's a dog--a big doggie!
Give me your paw! Down. Again.
[SHUGO] It really likes me!
[RENA] You really like animals
don't you, big brother?
It's too bad Mom was allergic
and we never got one.
I wonder where
it came from?
Do you think I can get one?
Uh, I don't remember reading
about there being any dog
raising here in The World.
I want one!
[BALMUNG] You want one?
Yeah, you bet!
[SHUGO]  Hey, I know you.
You're that guy
who saved us before.
That's Lord Balmung!
Whaddya mean...
"Lord" Balmung.
So, Kite...
and BlackRose...
That's right!
I've read about this before!
"Beneath the blooming cherry
trees are buried corpses!"
I haven't spotted any
conspicuous items nearby so,
if I unearth a corpse or two,
the cherries just have to bloom.
A character contest?
Yeah! It was a great victory.
My name is Rena.
The one here in the Kite costume
is my twin brother, Shugo!
Hello.
Rena... Shugo...
[BALMUNG]
That bracelet...
[SHUGO] Oh, this...
I got it... from
a girl all in white.
I guess there must
have been some kind of
special event attached
to this character.
She told me, "Only you
can save this world,"
then she gave this to me.
Please help...
[BALMUNG thinking]
Aura...?
[MIREILLE] Ah! I found it!
I knew I was right
about this one!
If I make the flowers bloom,
the rare item will be mine!
Ah... you gotta
be kiddin' me!
A Fighting Bones?
[SHUGO] Uhm... How come
you've been so quiet
for such a long time?
You can tell us,
if something is bothering you.
Or is it really that you want
this bracelet for yourself?
Hey, Shugo!
Don't insult Lord Balmung
after what he's done for us.
Hey, it was only a little joke!
[BALMUNG] If only it were...
Huh?
Lord Balmung,
I know it's a little late
but could you tell me something?
[BALMUNG] Mm?
Uh, back at the
dangerous spot the other day...
...when you came in
and saved me...
[MIREILLE]
Heeeelp!!
[MIREILLE] No way!!!
Mireille?
What's going on?
And why is there a
Fighting Bones here anyway?
Is it supposed to
be part of the event?
Impossible.
I never intended for there
to be monsters in this event!
Lord Balmung!
Reki? Was it you?!
It wasn't me, sir!
I don't have that
kind of time to waste!
[SHUGO] Is that monster strong?
[RENA] Insanely strong!
If they put one in here,
there'd be no way
for a newbie to enter.
Vak Revolver!
[BALMUNG] That can't be...
No way!
It's reviving!
[BALMUNG] Reki!
It's dangerous here!
Evacuate all player
characters from this area!
Yes, sir.
All of you should
get out of this area
as quickly as you can!
What's happening to this game?
Rena!
Oh, Shugo!
Shugo! Help!
Rena! Data... Drain!
Wh-Why can't I move my sword?
Could the Data Drain
be affecting
everyone in the immediate area?
[MIREILLE] This is for
scaring me half to death!
Vak Don! Vak Don! Vak Don!
Oh! Why won't my spells work?
Rena... Hey, are you all right?
Oh, my Shugo!
Eh?
I... really...
...LOVE YOU, Shugo!
Rena... What are
you doing? Stop it!
Oh, you are soooo brave.
Rena... you know...
we're brother and sister.
You're freaking me out.
[OHKA] Shugo!
Leave the rest to me!
Uh, who said that?
Oh...
Well, that was my
first transformation,
I guess I just blew
my cover completely, huh?
[MIREILLE] Ohka!
Ohka's fighting with us!
[SHUGO] She's a friend of yours?
[MIREILLE]
Yup! Divine Fist Ohka!
One of the most famous
melee fighters in The World!
She's INCREDIBLY strong!
[OHKA] Shugo, you know
you're wrong about one thing.
Eh?
Man, how brittle...
you must have
a calcium deficiency.
[OHKA] And I'm not
a dog I'm a wolf.
Actually I'm a
werewolf, to be specific.
You're a werewolf?
And I'm not
through with you yet!
Divine Fist Ohka...
There can be no doubt
she deserves her reputation.
So strong...
[MIREILLE] She truly
is Divine Fist Ohka!
The effects of the Data Drain
have finally worn off...
Uh, Shugo,
what am I doing here with you?
Rena? You're all right now?
[RENA] Put me down, Shugo!
Ok, I'll put you down but
you're the one that said, uh...
Oh, wow!
Strange things are
certainly happening
around Shugo and Rena again.
Oh, those limited-
edition characters!
Hey, Mireille!
Don't look now but...
It can't be!
Your spells you cast earlier
are finally taking effect.
Aww! The cherry trees!
That's it!
The Old Man Who
Made the Flowers Bloom!
The Old Man Who did what?
[SHUGO]
The old folk tale!
Upon the withered trees...
Let's make the flowers bloom!
Yes, that's correct!
[MIREILLE]
All right then!
Juk Rom!
Ahhh...
[REKI] I don't understand.
Why did the Fighting
Bones appear...?
Was it a data corruption?
Right now, too many
things are worrying me.
[BALMUNG]
But now...
Just for this moment...
Let us enjoy the
wondrous cherry blossoms.
[REKI] Uh... Yes, sir.
[MIREILLE] Ah! We found it!
We got the rare item!
Shugo was the one
that cleared today's
event, remember.
The item is his...
Ah! Rare item!!! I want it!!
I want it!! I want it!!
[MIREILLE] What is it?!
What is it?! What is it?!
Oooh...?
[OHKA] Chill out Mireille.
[SHUGO] Uh... What is this?
It looks kinda
like a dog collar...
That doesn't
make much sense.
Oh! It's about the Old Man
Who Made Flowers Bloom.
Hey, didn't he have a
dog in that story?
So this has to be its collar!
[SHUGO] Are you kidding me?!
What am I going to do with this?
You can't raise dogs
in The World, can you?
You could always...
...put it on me,
if you felt like it.
I wouldn't mind it... fly boy.
Uh, yeah... I don't...
That sounds like a good idea.
[RENA] Uh, Shugo!
I just remembered
I have to go make dinner!
Let's go, NOW!
That girl is certainly
serious about making dinner.
I'll treasure this
necklace always.
If you ever need me
just send me a message.
[RENA] I've got
information on items!
If you go to the area
Blazing Purgatory Valley
you can supposedly get a
hold of a Phoenix Feather.
Hey, Shugo, this is
your chance to be a hero!
...Or not.
Hey, who is that?!