[DOCTOR]
Blood Pressure decreasing.
Pulse decreasing.
There appears to be no
response to external stimulus.
[SHUGO'S FATHER]
You mean she's brain dead?
[DOCTOR] No, the brain
is still functioning.
She's still logged in?
[SHUGO'S MOTHER] Will
she return to normal?
[DOCTOR] This is very
unusual. I'm sorry,
but we're doing everything
that we can. It just...
[SHUGO] Why can't she log out?
[SHUGO] RENA!
[RENA]
I'm dead.
I'm dead. I'm dead. I'm dead.
[AURA] Please open your eyes.
[AURA] No.
You are not yet dead.
[RENA]
I'm dead.
Please open
your eyes, Rena.
[MIREILLE] What?!
Rena's been hospitalized?
How long has she been comatose?
And the doctors
don't have a clue why?
And when you say
she can't log out,
what do you mean
by that, exactly?
I wish I knew,
but then,
if she's still logged in,
she has to be
somewhere in The World.
She has to.
Rena's condition
in the real world
must be related to her
disappearance from here.
We have to keep looking around,
and maybe we can
find some kind of clue.
It's just that none of
this makes any sense.
And there's also that thing
back at the hot springs
to think about.
There's no way
that could have been
just a coincidence.
No doubt.
Something is behind all of this.
[SHUGO] And what if...
...we do manage to find her?
Do you think Rena will
regain consciousness
in real life?
We've got to keep trying.
Whoa!
[BALMUNG] Shugo?
What are you doing here?
Could you move your foot
before you keep talking?
Sanjuro. You're here.
So this is the area that
Rena disappeared from?
[BALMUNG] I checked
the access logs.
Since the time Rena
was killed in this area,
she hasn't logged out once.
That's a fact.
So you've already
started to investigate?
Impressive,
Mr. CC Corporation man.
But Rena. What
could've happened to her?
[crash]
Huh?
Who's there?
[REKI] Lord Balmung!
[SHUGO] Rena!
[screaming]
And now my second kiss
was wasted in a video game.
And with a guy this time.
[BALMUNG] Reki, why were you--
[REKI] What do you mean,
Lord Balmung?
You're the one that ordered me
to investigate this area,
if I remember.
So what did you find here?
Just some crazy kid
who likes to kiss people?
I wasn't talking about Shugo.
What about his sister?
Oh, yeah!
Uh...
There are definite traces
of a gate to this area
being forced opened
by someone outside.
Rena was...
...teleported to some
other area outside of here?
Teleported? To where?
[REKI] Any kind of
evidence of that
was cleanly deleted from
the system, I'm afraid.
[SANJURO] So we don't
know where she is?
Some administrators you are.
Administrate and investigate!
That's what I do every day
on behalf of the players
to maintain order in The World.
So he says...
But you have been
spending a lot of time
searching for our
friend Rena, haven't you?
It's not just for Rena
that I'm searching.
What do you mean... by that?
There are other users
who've been affected like this.
They've fallen into a
coma while logged in,
and are hospitalized
just like Rena.
In each case where something
like this has happened,
the users fell into a coma
while playing inside The World,
and all of those players
remained logged in.
This is in no way
some kind of system bug.
Someone evil is intent on
destroying this world,
and we will hunt them down,
make no mistake about that!
An evil intent. Huh.
[BALMUNG] I will not allow it!
Now, where's that Kite?
You mean Shugo.
[DAISUKE]
Whoever, doesn't matter.
Shugo. Kite. Who cares?
[KATSUYUKI] Looks like
he's loitering around
the Cursed Woodland
Murderhouse again.
[HAYATO]
His IQ's in the basement.
Come on. Why don't
we quit toying around
and start our plan
to get rid of him,
just like we did to BlackRose?
[MICHI] You mean Rena.
Oh, whatever her name is!
Balmung of the
Azure Sky is with them.
We can't do anything right now.
He'll be able to track us down.
You're right.
Hey! They just
came back to us!
The Twilight.
Oh. We can see
that, obviously.
[SANJURO] That's not it.
Huh?
The same thing happened
to a group of
players four years ago.
When it happened,
they called it the
Twilight Incident.
[BALMUNG]
Many users were injured,
and The World was on
the verge of destruction.
[BALMUNG] The ones
that resolved the incident
were not CC Corporation
administrators.
They were a party of players.
How come I've never heard
of that incident before?
It's not in any of
The World log files.
[SANJURO] CC Corporation
erased all the logs.
There are no
official records left
from that time in the game.
However, it was something
that actually happened.
The key players in bringing
about its successful resolution
were Kite and BlackRose.
Oh?
And from that point on,
they were known as the .hackers.
Did you say the .hackers?
I think I've heard of them.
Yeah, that party
was supposed to be
the one that solved the
last mystery of The World!
Well, maybe that's
what The World
thinks about it these days.
But that's all just
a rumor, I assure you.
So how...
do you know so much?
Because Balmung and
I were two original members
of the .hackers.
[KATSUYUKI] Well?
[HAYATO] It's no good.
I've lost them
[MICHI] Same here.
[DAISUKE] Aw, man!
Where did they go?
A hideout, maybe?
What is that?
It's a rare
item you can earn.
It'd be difficult to
sneak into one of those,
if that's what they're using.
Now what?
they'll have to pass through
a Chaos Gate eventually.
There's no need for us to go
out of our way to find them.
They'll have to come out
of there some time.
The enemy. They have been aware
of Shugo's existence
here from the very start.
Uh, me?
The enemy probably also knows of
the events from four years ago
and the main thing keeping them
from their objective
would be Kite's bracelet.
Huh? Oh...
From here on out, the
enemy will be pursuing you.
Understand, Shugo?
Huh?
[BALMUNG] So don't
act like a fool.
Huh?
You don't have
to be a jerk about it!
Rena.
I've never heard
that story before, Rena.
The story's true.
The rabbit in the moon is there
to give courage
to all travelers.
When the
traveler is in trouble,
it comes to save them!
Rena.
Okay.
Rena's a
traveler in trouble.
So I'll be the
rabbit who saves her!
[AURA] Please, open your eyes.
Please, open your eyes.
[RENA] I...
[AURA] Rena.
[RENA] Could you be...
...th-the rabbit?
My name is Aura.
Aura?
[RENA] Aura.
My broth--I mean,
Shugo said he'd met you.
[AURA] That's right.
[RENA] Oh, man.
Looks like I'm alive!
[AURA] Yes.
[RENA] But I was sure that
monster got me back there.
But wait,
that was inside the
game world, though, right?
I just need to log out and
sort things out in my head.
[RENA] Huh? Why can't I log out?
Is there...
some kind of bug?
The trance.
[RENA] Huh?
[AURA] When you were
defeated by the monster,
an evil suggestion
was placed in your mind.
You were in a trance,
under the suggestion
that you were dead.
[RENA] A trance?
[AURA] And because
of that influence,
in the real world,
[RENA] I died?
No, not yet.
[RENA] What do you mean?
Your life still hangs by a
thread back in the real world.
But if it's allowed
to remain in that state
for too much longer...
[RENA] I'm going to...
No. You are
not alone in this.
There are many others like
you trapped in this area,
who have had the
suggestion placed upon them
that they are dead,
and here they remain with me.
[RENA] So many of them.
But isn't there
something you can do
to help these trapped souls?
Like when you gave
Shugo that amazing bracelet.
Please!
[gasps]
My existence here
is but a shadowed one,
as you can now see.
It was all I could do
to awaken you from
the suggestion's hold.
So what can I do
to get outta here?
[AURA] There is only one hope.
The rabbit!
Leave it to me!
Have no fear, the
Legendary Hero is on the quest!
Rena!
[SHUGO]
Rena, wait for me!!
[KOMIYAN] Rena's here?
Tres bien!
[SHUGO] Gusting
Southern Nation Snows!
Gusting Southern Nation Snows!
[HAYATO] Party members?
[MICHI] Shugo's alone.
Hey, hey, hey.
You've got to let
me do it this time.
I made the coolest
monster to take him out.
[HAYATO] But why is he alone?
Who cares?
They'd all get
smashed along with him.
How high a level
did you make it?
Why ask something you
already know the answer to?
[KATSUYUKI] Okay, all right,
I'm leaving it to you.
[DAISUKE] Ya-ha!
[KATSUYUKI] All right, everyone.
Let's get ready.
Let's do it!
[OHKA] Can someone tell me
why Shugo's alone in this area?
[MIREILLE] Probably not looking
for a rare item, I guess.
[HOTARU] No doubt
he's looking for Rena.
[SHUGO yelling]
[SHUGO] Hello? Nice monster?
Ah! Whoa!
What is that?
A Killer Snake or a Moonlighter?
I've never
seen one of those!
[OHKA] It's a merge
of multiple creatures--
some sort of modified monster!
And now, to finish this!
[SHUGO] No!
Wait!
You can't kill it yet, Sanjuro!
The enemy is using this
monster to try to kill me.
Then, like Rena,
I'll be teleported through
an invisible gate
where no one can find me.
That's it!
Shugo.
There has to be a gate
connected to the area
where they're holding Rena.
If we can find it,
we can save her!
I get it!
So that's what they're doing!
[SHUGO]
There must be a something
in the monster's
programming code.
When the
monster is killed,
there must be something in
the code that opens the gate.
If we can just analyze it,
I can find out where Rena is!
[SANJURO] Shugo.
It seems there's no fear
of overkill with this one.
Shugo!
Data Drain it now!
Weaken it enough so
we can capture it alive.
I got it!
Data Drain!
[KOMIYAN]
Rena!
Komiyama?!
Data Drain!
[MIREILLE] Shugo, you don't
have enough skill points left!
Sanjuro and I can hold this
one off while you get clear!
[OHKA] I'll help!
I could use a good fight.
[SANJURO] Mireille, Hotaru!
Help Shugo recover
his skill points!
[MIREILLE] Okay!
[OHKA yelling]
[MIREILLE] Rig-gee-em,
rig-gee-em!
[MIREILLE] Wait!
Shugo! You haven't
recovered your skill points!
Hurry. They're all in trouble.
Hurry!
Hey, that feels much better.
Hurry.
Recovery complete!
All right! You're all set!
Yeah!
Data...Huh?
Who.. Who are they?
[BALMUNG] The Cerulean...
[SANJURO] ...Knights!
Formation Delta!
[BALMUNG] Stop!
You mustn't kill it!
[KAMUI] Delete!
Stop it!
If you delete it,
then Rena will...
Don't let your
heart blind you.
Operation complete.
Prepare to withdraw.
[BALMUNG] Kamui
Hey! They cheated!
[HAYATO] That's not cool!
Not bad.
Looks like CC Corporation's
finally getting serious, too.
Very interesting.
[SHUGO] Rena.
Kamui.
Lord Balmung.
Kamui!
Are you trying to tell
me that you still love me?
So those two,
something going on between them?
Dunno.
Why did you and your
knights interfere?
You had no
justification to be here!
You just destroyed our plan
to capture the modified monster
and find the missing players.
The plan to find your new love,
don't you mean, Balmung?
Oh, no!
There's no way that Balmung
could ever be Rena's boyfriend!
Well I have a new love, too,
so you don't have
to worry about it.
A new love?
Reki. You!
Love is blind, they say.
And one more thing,
this incident has
been transferred
to the control of
the Cerulean Knights
who are under my command.
It's a CC Corporation
upper division decision,
I'm afraid.
You should be getting your
email notification soon enough.
[BALMUNG] An incident like this
the corporation is going to
be transferring this to you?
If that's a problem,
send an email.
[KNIGHT A] Lady Kamui,
data maintenance is complete.
Good.
Prepare to move out!
You know I'll still
love you, Balmung,
as long as you
stay out of my way.
So what the heck
was that all about?
They suddenly show up
and ruin my
super-duper rescue plan
and then just
disappear like that?
They're the Cerulean Knights,
the CC Corporation's
counter net terrorism force.
[SANJURO] In other words,
their job is to
police the system
and to unmask
any terrorist threats.
Part of their job is to
not care about anyone else.
Then what about Rena?
[BALMUNG] It's not
their responsibility
to search for missing players.
So Lord Balmung!
These guys are your
friends, isn't that right?
You could pull
some strings, huh?
It's already...
Already...?
...too late.
Why's that?
Because of one thing.
One thing? What's that?
Because the sword cannot
win against the heart!
Huh?
[SHUGO] Stop joking around!
[SHUGO]
Rena.
[RENA] I have
secret information!
Hey, Shugo, did you know
that there used to
be a legendary group
called the Crimson Knights?
That means that the guy
with the glowing eyes is...
Whoa...