[FEMALE FIGHTER] Excuse me.
I have a little favor
I'd like to ask.
A favor... like what?
[FEMALE FIGHTER] Starting
tomorrow, well actually...
...actually it's later today,
I'll be going out of town
on a trip for three days.
So, during that time,
I'm afraid...
I'm afraid my
Grunty here will...
W-Well, he's going to be
alone, so I was wondering...
Ah!
Can you... watch him?
Uh... I-I really don't know...
It's only for three days.
Just three little
days to keep him safe.
Please, can you help me out?
Hungry, hungry!
Food, food food!
[MIREILLE] Ta da!
[SHUGO]
Uh...
Presenting Mireille's
secret room!
In other words,
a rare item storeroom.
Wow...
So you managed to get a
hidden room for your stuff?
This room is actually
a rare item itself!
But now...
...the one rare item I want
more than anything is...
[SHUGO]
Oooo...
What a nice
texture this has to it!
Let's get outta here.
C'mon Shugo.
Aaaahn, wait! Hang on!
I promise I'll never
say I want it ever again!
Well, it does sound
like an interesting place.
I suppose we can stay here for
a little bit longer, uh, okay?!
[RENA] Well?
So, whadya think?
It's just what
I thought I would find.
This bracelet is a
really high-level item.
How can you tell?
[MIREILLE] Look here.
The higher the level of an item,
the more resilient the materials
and the better the quality.
In terms of bracelets,
I'd say Shugo's is
the highest level item
you'll be able to
get in The World.
Whoa. This thing is?
[RENA and OHKA] Mireille!
I-It's not like I actually SAID
that I wanted it for my own.
Your eyes say it all.
[SHUGO] But if this is
such an incredible bracelet,
then why...?
Wh-Why can't I move my sword?
Could the Data
Drain be effecting
everyone in the immediate area?
This is for scaring
me half to death!
Vak Don! Vak Don! Vak Don!
Why don't my spells work?
Oh, you are soooo brave!
I wonder what the
bracelet did back there?
t was obviously your fault.
Mm-hmm.
What?
If a player wants to use
such a high-level item as
it was meant to be used,
the player must also be
of a sufficiently
high level, as well.
Um, so you're saying
I can't control this thing?
Exactly!
Let's go get you trained!
[SHUGO] Right now?
[RENA] This is a
mid-class level area.
[SHUGO] But I...
I'm still a newbie.
[MIREILLE] Don't worry, Shugo.
I'm with you.
[SHUGO] Great.
Let's... GO!
All right! Let's have some fun!
[RENA] Yeah! You're on!
Hey!
Hey, Wait... for me.
Ah, a Squilla Demon!
Easy Win! Easy Win!
Vak Don!
You're in the way!
Big brother!
Shugo, you just stay back!
But I thought I was the one
who needed to fight to
level up in the first place.
It's all right!
All right? Huh...?
I've leveled up?
Is that right?
See? You don't have to
defeat an enemy directly,
you just have to
be a part of the fight
and then your level
will go up, too.
So, you can just sort of
swing your sword around
at the enemy's back.
Isn't this an easy
way to train, Shugo?
Huh...?
[BALMUNG]
Is that... for certain...?
[REKI] Yes.
I've checked many things,
but I only have some
vague conclusions.
Someone did open the
character campaign page,
but it's not clear who
that might have been.
[BALMUNG] What about
the system administrators?
I was sure to
check with them, too.
They informed me that they had
no specific answers for
me regarding the matter.
[BALMUNG] Then report
it as a Level One claim.
That should get a
reaction from someone.
Yes sir, understood.
[BALMUNG thinking]
Those two... It can't be...
[REKI] Lord Balmung...
Is this a puzzle
for today's event?
[BALMUNG]
Bamboo grass means pandas.
And in Japanese, "Pan - Da"
means: "It's - bread."
[OHKA]
Come here!
[MIREILLE] You're amazing,
Divine Fist Ohka!
Vak Don!
You still have a lot to learn.
Never let your guard down.
And never move
in a straight line,
just move side to side.
Right! Got it!
[MIREILLE]
I'll get you all! Vak Don!
[SHUGO] Oh, wow! I can actually
feel myself getting stronger!
Ha! There's no doubt about it!
I'm leveling up like crazy.
[RENA] Ohka, you're the coolest!
[SHUGO] Rena! I'm amazing!
[RENA] I still have
a long way to go.
At least I'm happy about it.
[RENA] Hey, Shugo, you've
leveled up quite a bit.
[SHUGO] You... really think so?
[OHKA] You've still
got a long ways to go.
Compared to Ohka,
a loong waaay!
Hmph.  I think
it's safe to say...
...you do, too, Rena.
Actually, Rena's level is much
higher than yours is, Shugo.
Huh? How can that be?
We started at
the exact same time.
Well, I've been doing a lot
of extra training in secret
when you weren't around, Shugo.
That's not fair.
Pretty sneaky, too
[RENA chuckles] Sorry.
[SHUGO] Hey! A treasure chest!
No, Shugo! Hang on!
[SHUGO cries out]
You should never rush to
open a trapped treasure chest.
You okay?
Well, that was
a level down trap.
Huh?
Well, Shugo, I'm afraid
you're back down to level one.
Level one?
Well, it's time to pick
yourself back up and try again.
Ugggh! I can't stand this!
Shugo, no!
Oh, man...
Why'd that girl ever choose me?
And why did she
give this thing to me?
[GRUNTY sneezes]
Huh? Hey... Is your pet sick?
Yes, he's sick!
And I don't know what to do!
[SHUGO] So you were asked
by a complete stranger...
[HOTARU] My name is
Hotaru, by the way,
and I've never
raised a Grunty before.
[SHUGO] Don't you have
any friends you can call?
[HOTARU] I do have one.
He's very dependable,
b-but I haven't
seen him at all today.
So it looks like
we're at a loss, huh?
[GRUNTY RANCHER]
Hmm. Oh! This is terrible.
This one definitely
has the Grunty Flu.
Didn't you have it vaccinated
for this type of thing?
It's a terrible sickness
for the little guy.
If you don't do anything for it,
it's going to die
within a few hours.
[gasps]
Well, there has to be a
way that we can save it!
The only medication for
this is the "Phoenix Feather."
And the only place one
can be found is far away,
deep within the dungeons of
the Blazing Purgatory Valley.
[SHUGO] Eh?
Do you know what
that area is like?
It's a pretty high level area.
It'll be an extremely
difficult quest for a newbie.
Should we... go?
It'll be fine.
I have strong friends
that can help us out!
[MOTHER]
Rena, you're at it again,
you've been playing
since lunchtime!
[RENA] But Mom, today's Sunday!
I can do anything I want!
[MOTHER] You play all week too!
Your school called and said
that you've been
cutting class a lot lately.
I'm not having any luck getting
in touch with anyone today.
How about you?
Nuh-uh. No one.
[GRUNTY whines]
Then we'll do it alone.
It's up to us!
[SHUGO] Blazing...
[SHUGO and HOTARU]
...Purgatory Valley.
Is this the place?
All right, Fairy's Orb!
[HOTARU] What do
those marks tell us?
Ah, that's where monsters
are likely to come out.
[SHUGO] At our level,
if we fight the monsters here,
there's not much chance
we're gonna survive.
Now we have... this! Now this
thing is a Speed Charm.
It really speeds you up.
And, if we run into a monster,
we'll just use it to get away.
Mmm. I understand.
[SHUGO]
Pheeew! C'mon! This way!
Hey! It's a puppy!
So high...
[SHUGO] Hotaru...
Huh?
[HOTARU] Shugo!
[HOTARU skrieks]
Hotaru!
[SHUGO] This is not good!
It's a dead end!
We've gotta get outta here!
[HOTARU] We can't!
[SHUGO] Eh?
If we just turn
around now, that...
that little Grunty is
surely going to die.
Ohhh...
We can't let it die.
That little guy's
counting on us.
Yeah, you're right.
Shugo! Shugo,
are you all right?
I think so.
[SHUGO thinking]
If we use this...
But that's no good!
If it fails what will we do?
I'm still only level 1!
[HOTARU]
Stop!
A Grunty is going
to die without our help.
Please let us pass for its sake!
Hotaru! Get outta there!
Please listen to me!
[gasps]
[SHUGO] Data Drain!
Aw! Yes!
Shugo, look!
What are you
doing playing around
with small fries
like these, Kite?
Eh?
Oh, Sanjuro!
Hey, I got your
email and raced here.
But if Kite is here with you,
there should be no worries
in a place like this.
I'm not... My name's not Kite.
S'cuse me?
My name is... Shugo!
Shugo?
[SANJURO] I see...
So, you were the winner
of a character contest.
CC Corporation certainly
was most generous with you.
Ah!
The Phoenix Feather! This is it!
We did it!
He's just so playful...
[SANJURO] He seems to
really like you, Hotaru.
[HOTARU] You think so?
That makes me so happy...
[SHUGO] Yeah, you guys
look really good together.
[FEMALE FIGHTER]
What's going on?
He sounds so happy...
How cool, he's okay!
He's alive!
He looked like he'd
caught something
before I left and
I thought he was a goner.
So you knew? Then left?
Ah!
I can't thank you enough
for taking care of him!
Come here little guy!
He says he doesn't
want to go back with you.
[SANJURO] Caring for it
only when it's healthy,
then throwing it away
when circumstances
take a turn for the worse.
Do you think someone
like that is qualified
to call themselves an owner?
[SHUGO] That's right!
The responsibilities
and obligations
of my own life are more
than enough work for me.
You can't expect to act
like that in a game, too.
It's just a Grunty, you guys.
JUST a Grunty, huh?
Do you have any idea what we had
to do to save this
little guy's life?!
Shugo...
Enough... Shugo.
[RENA] Hey, brother!
Rena!
Huh?
Sorry to make you wait.
Me, too.
Hey, who are these characters?
Who us?
Well, we're the ones
who were called
in just now on behalf
of "just a Grunty"!
Disappointing...
...that someone like
you could be an owner.
You're not even worthy
of being called a gamer.
[OHKA] You're coming with us.
[FEMALE FIGHTER] Hey, wait a
sec! What are you going to do?
[OHKA] We need to teach
you a little something
about how to treat others.
[FEMALE FIGHTER]
Can't we all just get along?
We should all be enjoying
this together... Friends?
You're gonna have to
give us just a minute.
[OHKA]
Hey, what do you think of that?
[FEMALE FIGHTER]
Hey, what are you doing to me?
[SANJURO] Uh...
[OHKA sighs] I feel
much better now...
[MIREILLE] Ah!
I always feel refreshed
when I do a good deed...
[RENA] Yep.
So, what just
happened back there?
I think it's better if we
don't know the details.
Where is...
Does anybody know
where Sanjuro went to?
Huh?
[SANJURO] It seems
that you've found
employment at the
CC Corporation...
I guess I should
congratulate you... Balmung.
It's not something
I'm happy about.
In any event, I have
a favor to ask of you.
[SANJURO]
Hmm?
Shugo, that new character
that looks exactly like Kite,
I want you to
start training him.
[SANJURO] Hmm... What for?
I'm afraid I'm not able to
elaborate right now. Except...
Twilight is drawing
ever more near...
...and that boy holds the key.
[SANJURO gasps]
Understood!
[RENA] I have event information!
In the area Distant Azure River
is the Festival of
the Weaver Maiden.
Hmmm. What should I wish for...
Uh, I'm the Weaver Maiden?
And I have to kiss
my brother?! Blech!