[alarm]
Aww, man. They can't be
performing maintenance
for twenty-four hours
straight on this server.
Ahh... This time the
Spring of Myst is empty!
Who's behind this prank?
[surprised yelp]
What kind of
monster was that?
Upside down palm trees,
empty Springs of Myst,
unheard of monsters...
This is crazy!
How is this happening?
[TOM screams]
Gotta log out
and contact the
system administrator.
Eh...? What's happening?!
[SHUGO] I, Shugo Kunisaki,
upon entering junior high,
thought I had outgrown games.
[ANNOUNCER] Congratulations!
[SHUGO] I knew that a net game
called "The World"
was really popular,
but I never had
a desire to play it
[ANNOUNCER] You've won
the grand prize in the
The World Limited-
Edition Character Contest
[SHUGO] Until today, that is.
[RENA] What? You're kidding me.
You won the contest, too?
Whaddya mean "won"?
You mean you just went
behind my back and entered me?
Rena, how could you do this?
[RENA] But the odds
are astronomical
for the two of us
to have won together!
Aren't you glad I did?
Aw, man, we're definitely twins!
[SHUGO] But Rena...
Even if I did win this...
I don't have the
software for The World.
[RENA] No Problem!
Before Mom and
I left your place,
I installed it on your computer.
[SHUGO] Eh? You did what?
[RENA] And, since we
both won the same contest,
we can explore
The World together!
[SHUGO] She's got an
answer for everything.
[SHUGO] Well, here goes nothin'.
Oooooh! Oooh, hah!
Wow, this is a net game?
They sure are
getting more realistic.
[PC#1] Hey, I don't
see you for a while
and you've suddenly leveled?
[PC#2] It's 'cause
I've been sticking
with a strong party.
I've gained a lot of
experience with this spear.
[PC#3] Yeah!
That area's treasure
boxes are mostly trapped!
[MACHO PC] Hey, wanna
form a party with me?
[SHUGO] Uuuuungh!!
[GLAMOROUS HEAVY BLADE]
You have some nerve
plowing into me like that.
So what do you have
to say for yourself?
[GLAMOROUS HEAVY BLADE]
You wanna try it again?
Yeah, right...
[SHUGO] I... uh, just might
get to like The World.
[RENA] Shugo, you're late!
You're my brother Shugo, right?
Whoa! C-Could you be... Rena?
My little twin sister... Rena?
Is it you?
Bingo! It's sure been
a while, big brother.
And, it's our first time
meeting in character...
I'm Rena the Heavy Blade!
Nice to meet you.
Thanks...
Those two...
Aren't they the ones?
Y'mean...
...the limited-edition
characters?
You're kidding...
They're the winners?
[PC#6] Don't they
look a little small
to be the legendary heroes.
[PC#5] Yeah, they sure do.
[PC#1] You just don't see
those characters around anymore.
[SHUGO] Don't look now,
but I think we've been noticed.
[RENA] Well, of course!
We're the winners of the
Character Campaign Contest.
So cool! I never
thought that the
.hacker characters
would be the prize...
...we're so lucky!
Who are the ".hackers"?
In the game,
they were the party that solved
the Last Mystery of The World
and because of that
they became legends.
There were
two original members:
a young male Twin Blade, Kite
and a young girl
Heavy Blade, BlackRose.
And when they
solved the mystery,
other players weren't allowed
to use their
character forms anymore.
Now we get to look like
the legendary heroes...
It's so cool!
We look like
legendary heroes...?
[RENA] What's wrong?
[SHUGO] Y-Your outfit...
It's kinda...
Can't you do something about it?
[RENA] Eh?!
It's just...
Couldn't you wear something
a little more legendary?
[RENA] I don't know...
Personally, I think
this look is kinda cute
[SHUGO] Even if
it's just a game...
It's making me a
little uncomfortable.
[RENA] Oh, well you
just need to get over it!
I've found you!
[HOTARU] Um, excuse me...
[HOTARU] W-Would you...
do business with me...?
[SANJURO] Fairly sudden to ask
to do business with someone...
M-My mistake.
I mean... I can...
come back... if you want.
[HOTARU] Um... or...
I-I could just...
Just relax, lttlie one.
I'll do business with you...
[SHUGO] It's so strange
talking with Rena three
months after she's left.
Have you...
been eating okay?
Huh? Eh? Yeah!
Y'know, I've actually
become a pretty good cook.
[SHUGO] What about you?
Is mom keeping busy with work?
I guess.
[SHUGO] Yeah, well...
Hey, since we're
logged into The World,
let's do something.
But what's wrong
with chatting?
That can be fun, too.
[SHUGO] Come on! Let's go!
Alright, I'm coming!
Let's get down to the basics of
role-playing: fighting monsters!
[SHUGO] Alright!
[RENA] Okay ready?!
Bursting...
Passed Over... Aqua Field!
[MIREILLE] Bursting
Passed Over Aqua Field!
[RENA] Here we are!
Where are the monsters?
They appear through
these magic portals.
Magic portals?
[RENA] This way. C'mon!
[SHUGO] Hey, Rena! Wait up!
[RENA] C'mon slow poke!
This is a
beginner level...
It's an area designed
for newbie characters.
But those two are...
[RENA] Okay, here it comes
You'll be just fine,
you don't need
to be that nervous!
The monsters are usually
just small fries in this area.
[SHUGO] That's... A monster?
[RENA] That's a Mad Grass.
It's a level one monster.
Level One?
Yeah.
Stand back, Rena...
I'll protect
my fair little sister!
Go, Shugo!
Be careful!
Calamity Cut!
[RENA] The legendary
hero is crying.
Here, take this.
[SHUGO] Huh?
[RENA] It's a health drink.
It restores your hit points.
[SHUGO]
Phew... That really helps!
Shugo, you have no idea
how to attack, do you?
Eh?!
You could've just used a
simple blade attack against
a Mad Grass and
defeated it easily.
You know what I think?
You didn't read the manual...
After all I went through.
[RENA] Hey, Shugo!
You say you've
graduated from games,
but in reality, you never
read the instruction manual
and then just play
however you want.
Then you complain
when you get defeated
and stop playing.
That's not graduating.
Isn't that more like quitting?
I wouldn't go that far...
[RENA] Look, that's fine
with those other games.
But this game is The World...
And don't forget I can
actually see you in here...
Ok, I'll read the manual.
The next monster's mine
and that one doesn't
stand a chance!
[SHUGO] This time, for sure!
[RENA] The legendary hero.
He's back in the game.
Uh, is this one of
those "small fry" monsters?
No it's, an
Armored Super Shogun!
That's a level 48 super
strong monster here.
[BOTH] Waugh!
[MIREILLE] Whoa...
What in The World is
an Armored Super Shogun
doing in a newbie area?!
[SHUGO] Rena!
I'm dying just from that?
Shugo! You need to heal.
There's no time!
But you'll...
[SHUGO] Get outta here!
Run!
[SHUGO] I was finished
off... like that?
Man, just when I wanted
to prove myself to Rena...
What kind of game is this?
[SHUGO] What is this?
Is this part of The World too?
[SHUGO] Am I dead?
I wonder what happens
when you die in this game?
Well, it's just a game, right?
All I have to do is get this
Head Mounted Display off, right?
[SHUGO] Wh-What?
I can't move!
Somebody help me!
Dad! Mom! Rena!!!
[RENA] Hey Shugo!
Where are you, Shugo?
[RENA] Shugo... Where are you?
As long as
there's someone...
As long as there's someone
still alive in the party...
...a character
who dies is supposed
to remain nearby as a ghost!
So where is he then?
Something's wrong!
[RENA] How could such
a powerful monster
appear in this area?!
There's nothing about this
in the instruction manual!
[RENA]
Ahhhhh!!
[AURA] You mustn't die...
[SHUGO] Rena...?
No... Who is this?
Aaah! Well thank you.
So you've healed
all my damage?
[AURA] Data Drain...
Huh?
You can
defeat it using...
...Data Drain.
I can defeat it...?
That monster?
The only one who
can save The World...
...that one is you.
You are the heir
to the .hackers legend
Uh-hey... Wait!
[AURA] Please help.
I'm alive... Right?
That was my first kiss...
Hmm? This bracelet...
Noooo!
Rena!
Renaaaaa!
[gasps]
Balmung of the Azure Sky?!
What?
Owww...
Rena! RENAAAA!
Shugo!
Just keep back!
You're no match for this one!
[SHUGO] My little
sister is in trouble!
You think I'm gonna do nothing?!
[RENA] Shugo!
Rena!
Shugo!
Hang on!!
[SHUGO] I've gotta help
Rena! Data Drain!
The Armored Super Shogun
is now a Limp Knife!
Rena, you okay?! Huh?
Are you all right?
A... Ah... I am now...
Hey! Who are you?!
A-And you have no right...
...to hold my sister like that.
Who was that cool guy? Rawr...
A Limp Knife
is all that's left.
Vak Don!!!
The Rare Hunter
of Love and Courage
at your service.
Mireille's here!
Rare Hunter?
She plays a
Wavemaster character
that lives to
collect rare items.
Pleased to meet you.
You're the winners of the
limited-edition
characters, correct?
Uh... yes
[MIREILLE] I thought so!
I was sure that was it,
so I followed you!
[SHUGO] Huh...?
[MIREILLE] Thanks to you,
I got to see some
amazing things--
an Armored Super Shogun
appearing in a newbie area...
The appearance of Balmung
of the Azure Sky...
Did you say Balmung?
That guy who saved
us was Balmung?
Yup! He's a
legend in The World.
Ohhh... I forgot to thank him...
[MIREILLE] I guess you really
get some special events
when you're playing with
limited-edition characters!
[SHUGO thinking] Event...
Is that what that was?
But the biggest surprise
I've seen so far is
this amazing bracelet!
It's the first time
I've ever seen an item
that's able to rewrite
a monster's data.
Aaaah... nice texture...
It's so nice... It's so nice...
[RENA] C'mon Shugo!
I have to make dinner!
[RENA] Let's go home...
[SHUGO] Uh... Ok...
Bye then. See ya!
Thanks
Ah! Hold on a second!
[REKI] You called, Lord Balmung?
[BALMUNG] Reki, just now,
an Armored Super Shogun
appeared in this area...
That can't be!
This is an area for beginners.
[BALMUNG]
It was slightly different
from the typical
Armored Super Shogun.
Eh?
[BALMUNG] Perhaps...
...it has something to
do with that incident.
I understand.
I'll go investigate
[BALMUNG] But...
What worries me
more is those two.
Kite and BlackRose...
Why have those
two characters returned?
[RENA] Hey there!
I've got information
on upcoming events!
You can "Flower View"
in the area
"Voluptuous Cherry Maze."
So, don't forget to bring
some sweet dumplings." Okay?
Hey, Shugo! Forget that dog!