[SHUGO screaming]
Don't run away.
Yaaah! Here I go!
[SANJURO] Now it's your turn.
[SHUGO] Aaaaaah!
You can do it...
The pain...
[RENA] Heeey!
Hey Shugo.
Rena!
Lately, all you've
been doing is playing
with Sanjuro and not with me.
We've been training,
not playing...
All great warriors must first
learn to train properly.
Yeah, but he's not a warrior!
I want to become stronger!
So I can protect you!
It's all right if you train,
but we need to spend some
time together, too, y'know.
Mm. Yeah.
[SHUGO] Night of
the Weaver Festival...?
[RENA] That's right.
Tonight, over in a special area,
the Night of the Weaver
Festival event is being held!
Well... what's that?
Well, let's be sure
to check it out...
...plus it's "Tanabata Night"...
The holiday when
the lovers Orihime
and Kengyu are reunited.
This event is bound to be a
wonderfully romantic adventure!
Romantic?
And what's so wrong
with being romantic?
[KOMIYAN]
Shishishishishi.
To not understand the
romance of Tanabata Night...
Oh-ho, what a fool!
Bonjour, Mademoiselle.
Shishishishi.
Ah, why don't you
leave that boorish guy
and go with me to
this romantic event?
Shishishishi!
Whoa! Oof!
And who... are you?
I am Komiyan the Third...
I am known as the
King of Aloofness!
Shishishishi!
Uh-huh. You're Komiyama, right?
[KOMIYAN gasps loudly]
Ouchouchouchouch!
Yup, he's Komiyama.
Do not speak of
the real world here!
And who are you anyway?
Hey, it's Shugo Kunisaki
[SANJURO]
An acquaintance of yours?
He used to be in
my class last year.
It was that ridiculous
laugh that gave him away.
Hey, is it really Komiyama?!
Remember me, Rena?!
Uh... Th-The same
Rena that transferred out?
Yeah... that's me!
[KOMIYAN sucks air in]
Ohhh.. Ooo... Mmmm!
Even inside a game
Rena is tres bi-eeeehn!!
Ouch.
[SHUGO] Don't be hitting
on game characters.
Come on, Rena, let's find
Mireille and the others.
Uh?
Then I'll sign up for the
Tanabata Event tonight.
Really?!
I'm sorry.
Were you in the middle of
maintenance, Lord Balmung?
Tonight's event will be
getting underway very soon.
Reki, I'm leaving
tonight's event up to you.
What, Lord Balmung?
It's not a bad thing to
occasionally return to being
just a normal player and
sign up for the event, is it?
You just want
to play, don't you?
[BALMUNG] Hm.
Uh, did something...
happen today?
[BALMUNG] The other day,
it seems an operator
in the middle of maintenance
slipped into a coma...
[REKI] What?! But
how could that happen?
The Twilight.
But that's not possible
since everyone knows
the system was improved
so an event like that
could never happen again!
[BALMUNG] But even this system
is still not
completely error free...
When we receive information
regarding disturbances,
we operators need to be
acting on them immediately.
[REKI] Lord Blamung...?
[BALMUNG] A perfect
version of The World
might well be unattainable.
Sorry I'm late!
Whoa! A yukata!
It's Mireille's prized secret...
It's a very rare item!
Sorry we're late.
Ooh! Everyone's in a yukata!
Hey, Mireille, what's so rare
about your yukata anyway?
Ugh! I got it
from a major battle!
It's different
from everyone else's!
Oh really?
[RENA] Shugo...
Huh?
[chuckles] Does it... suit me?
Oh. Uh-huh.
I'm so relieved!
And what do you think
about mine, Shugo?
Does it suit me?
Uh... yeah.
Kay!
Little space here,
a little space.
Now we're ready for Distant
Azure River, so let's GO!
[HOTARU] So, uh, what
are we doing exactly?
The Festival...
of the Weaver Maiden!
Huh?
You write down your wish
and dangle it from the trees.
If you do so,
it's said that your
wish will come true.
Oh, how neat!
Hmm... Hm? Hmmmm....
[OHKA] Yes.
Shugo! This is mine.
[KOMIYAN]
Shishishishi.
I've been waiting, Rena.
Hey, what are you
doing here, Komiyama?!
Uh... Is that you, Kunisaki?!
Course it is!
You think I'd leave my
little sister Rena alone
with someone like you around?!
[MIREILLE] An Acquaintance?
[RENA] Mm-hmm.
He's an old classmate.
Oh dear, you're
with friends, are you?
Their presence
here serves only
to enhance the beauty
of the fabulous Rena.
I'll delete him!
[REKI] All participants,
please gather around
the special event stage.
[REKI] Everyone, welcome
to the Azure Distant River!
This is the
Tanabata Night Event.
In honor of the
legendary Orihime,
this is a Battle Royale!
Or you could call it,
the Tanabata de Ton-O-Boat-A's!
Wow, that title's
all washed up...
Yeah, that joke is sinking fast.
[SHUGO] Yeah, I think
it's all wet, too...
I just don't understand
this kid's style...
[REKI] To start off,
one player will be chosen
to serve as "Orihime"
the legendary damsel.
After overcoming
a number of trials,
the one that reaches Orihime
first, will be the winner.
The prize for winner?
The wish that they
wrote down in secret
and hung from the
trees will come true!
So whattya think, folks?!
Seriously?!
Cool...
[KOMIYAN] Shishishi!
Oh, yes!
Rena's socks are mine!
If it is a wish that
cannot be fulfilled
within the boundaries
of The World,
a one-year access subscription
will be awarded to the winner.
[REKI] Okay! Is everyone ready?!
And our Orihime
is this lucky player!
Oh!
Rena!
What?!
And now, Orihime,
please introduce yourself!
Eh...? I'm, uh...
Rena, fourteen years old!
Pleased to meet you everyone!
[REKI]
Isn't that great folks?
[BALMUNG thinking]
The selection of Orihime should
have been completely random...
Yet, that's the girl
who was selected...
Can this be a coincidence...?
Oh, Rena!
Stand back!
The stage is moving!
This is the story of
Orihime and Kengyu.
They are fated to meet
for only one brief
moment each year...
...on the seventh night
of the seventh month...
[KOMIYAN] Oh, Rena,
I'm on my way!
There is no way
I'm letting that
guy win this event!
Rare item... Rare item...
Itching to go.
You're just watching?
A master works that way.
Fair enough.
If trained, Shugo has the
potential to improve even more.
[REKI] Now, cross
the River of Heaven
to reach the side of
your beloved Orihime!
[REKI] Let's go!
Rena!
You'll find the lake
gets deeper in the middle.
Please be careful.
You could have said so!
[KOMIYAN]
Oh, so clumsy, Kunisaki.
[SHUGO]
Hey, that's not fair!
[KOMIYAN] There's no rule
against riding a Grunty!
Shishishishi! Go,
my beloved mount, Oscar!
I'm not letting
that guy get to Rena!
I'm really sorry Shugo,
this race is mine!
[OHKA] Outta the way!
Eh?!
And now... Ice Storm!
Ice!
Yahoo!
Rare item... my ice skates! Wee!
What a relief this is!
[OHKA] Ugh! Mireille!
[MIREILLE] This is a cinch.
Not so fast!
[ice cracking]
Arrrgh! Ahahaha!!
Oh!
Sorry, nothing
personal, Mireille!
Let's go, Oscar!
Wait up!
[HOTARU] Someone help me!
Huh?
[SHUGO] Hotaru! What's wrong?!
I never learned how to swim.
Oh no!
I thought I'd make it...
If I could just stay on the ice.
Come on, Hotaru.
Let's head back.
[REKI] Oh my,
for some reason one
of the players
has turned around.
Shugo...
[REKI] In front
are Mireille and Ohka!
But coming up steadily behind
them is Komiyan the Third!
Don't get in my way, Ohka!
Don't you get in my way!
Back off!
[KOMIYAN]
Shishishishi.
I'm going to
profit from their fight,
and then the beautiful
Rena's socks will be mine!
[REKI] And now Komiyan
the Third takes the lead!
The others are behind
him by a sizable margin.
Will the winner indeed
be Komiyan the Third?!
What?!
Anyone but him!
I've got to stop
that fool right now!
Re-NAAAA!
I'm coming for you!
My darling Re-NAAAAA!
[REKI] Of course it's not
that simple to reach the goal!
It's time for the
monster to appear!
Wha...?!
It's a special monster
just for the event!
If we defeat it,
we're sure to get
a rare item for sure!
It's a high-level
special event monster!
At last a worthy foe!
[BOTH] Attack!
[MIREILLE] Vak Don!!!
[OHKA] What?!
It's not even scratched!
No way!
Eh?
Ah?!
What's this?
Is it the same as before?
Shugo!
Whoa! Glad to see you!
Never let your
guard down, Shugo.
Is that...?
It's Lord Balmung!
Ion Strike!
So...
[BALMUNG] No!
Rena!
[SANJURO thinking] Shugo...
Only you can defeat it...
Oh...
Shishishi.
Now's my opportunity...
[RENA] Save me, Shugo!
Renaaaaaaa!
[SHUGO] Data... Drain!
Aieeee!
We did it!
That was outstanding, Shugo!
Hey, these are
rare items and I got 'em!
[BALMUNG] Reki, good work!
[SHUGO] Rena!
Rena! You all right?
Rena!
Thank you Lord Balmung,
for bravely saving me
from danger one more time.
How will I ever repay you?
Rena?
And now for the winner!
Congratulations Lord Balmung!
What's that?
Reki, what's the
meaning of this?
Didn't you say to me that
I was not to stop this event
no matter what the
circumstances, Lord Balmung?
So the race was still going on?
Now before we award
the prize for the event,
Lord Balmung, the winner, will
receive a kiss from our Orihime.
Eh?
Reki!
What was that?!
I simply followed
Lord Balmung's rules
and they are very clear about
the winner receiving a kiss.
[SHUGO] Whoa!
So how 'bout that kiss?
Oho, it looks like there
was a photo finish
in today's event.
We're about to see a shot
taken at the finish line.
[REKI] Oh! By a
mere point one seconds,
Shugo reached the goal first!
Shugo is the winner!
I am?
You're entitled to
the special prize
of a kiss from
Orihime to the winner.
What?
Uhm...
[REKI] Come on now, quickly.
[SHUGO] But, she's my sister...
[REKI] It doesn't
matter, come on,
we're all waiting...
So, uh, what should we do?
I guess we just
have to do this.
[cheering, whistling]
[gulps]
Huh?
[MIREILLE] Nonononono!
There was no forecast for
rain tonight on this server...
This isn't right.
Reki, stop the
event right now!
[REKI] But... But, sir, I...
Before anything else
unexpected begins happening,
you need to evacuate all
the participants immediately!
[REKI] The event
for the Festival
of the Weaver Maiden
is now over!
We will contact the winners
via the message board
in the very near future.
Thank you all!
It's really
raining--let's go home!
Uh, good idea!
Hey, Shugo?
So tell me what it is that
you wished for big brother.
[SHUGO] It's a secret.
[RENA] Big brothers can
be so weird sometimes.
[RENA] I've got
event information!
If you go to the area
Cursed Woodland Murderhouse
something will happen...
What do you mean by "something"?
What? Save me, Shugo!!