[MORTI] Death to all
Player Characters.
And a "true death" will
come to this world...
[BALMUNG] Fireball Storm!
[MONSTER growling]
[SANJURO] Thunderbolt!
[OHKA] Absolute Zero!
[MIREILLE]
Raining Rocks!
N-No way!
Our items aren't
having any effect!
[MIREILLE] Aw! That virus is
ruining my rare costume!
[OHKA] At this rate,
before we destroy it,
we'll all be ruined!
[RENA] Uh, Shugo...
[SHUGO] There's no way...!
[KOMIYAN] K-Kunisaki!
[SHUGO] How did...
Why're you still here?
[KOMIYAN] Still here?
Where is this place?
Where's the Chaos Gate
outta here?!
[SHUGO] Sorry, I don't have
time to chat with you now!
[KOMIYAN] Hey!
What happened to your outfit?
Did you get some weird curse
cast on you or somethin'?
[SHUGO] Wha?
[SHUGO] Komiyama, how come
your costume isn't infected?
[KOMIYAN] What does that mean?
[SHUGO] You know Rena's
member address, right?
[KOMIYAN] Of course!
I send her daily emails
about my great adventures!
[SHUGO] Then...
Why aren't you infected
with the virus like all of us?
[KOMIYAN] A Virus?
[KAMUI] Maybe you'll
like some Night Fear!
[MONSTER growling]
[HOTARU] Or try this,
The Hanged Man!
[KAMUI] It worked!
[BALMUNG] Together,
while we have a chance!
[SANJURO] Quickly!
[MIREILLE] It's no use!
[OHKA] Mireille!
[MIREILLE] There's no way
we can defeat that horror.
We're all going to
die here for sure!
[BALMUNG] Never give up!
[MIREILLE] Everyone's
going to die...
[BALMUNG] Form up,
and we'll attack as a team!
[KAMUI] The creature
has to have a weakness!
[MICHI] Something that seeks
to transcend death itself
would not have any weaknesses...
[SHUGO] Don't give up!
[SHUGO] Rena... and
Aura...they're still fighting!
[RENA] Sh-Shugo...
[SHUGO] We can't
just give up the fight
here when we're so close!
[MIREILLE] But our
most powerful attacks
aren't even denting that thing!
And we're all running
out of items to use.
[SHUGO] There is one other way.
[HOTARU] But we've
tried everything...
What's left?
[SHUGO] Data Drain!
[AURA] No! You... mustn't...
[MICHI] How foolish can you be?
[OHKA] If you Data Drain
and Rena is hit,
think about the virus!
It could accelerate
and destroy us all!
She's part of that
monster, don't forget.
[SHUGO] Nobody said that I was
going to use it on the monster.
[KOMIYAN] Hey!
You don't have
to be so rough!
[HOTARU] Hey, look it's...
[RENA] K-Komiyama...
[KAMUI] What use is he?
[KOMIYAN] Huh? Rena!
What are you doing in there?!
[KOMIYAN]
What's wrong with her?!
[SHUGO] I learned
that Komiyama
exchanged member
addresses with Rena.
But as you can see,
unlike us,
he's not affected
by the virus at all.
[SHUGO] And then
I started to think...
why he of all people
would be all right!
And then it came to me!
[SHUGO] It was the Data Drain!
I remember you
were Data Drained
when you got in
the way of my attack.
[SHUGO] Something
about the Data Drain
made you immune to the virus,
that's why I think
it's the answer now.
[AURA]
That possibility exists...
[SANJURO] Shugo, you
can't be thinking about
Data Draining all of us?
[SHUGO] If I stop in time,
I might be able to
weaken the virus enough
to keep it from
causing any more damage.
Maybe then we'll have a chance
to defeat that thing
once and for all.
[MIREILLE] It's too dangerous!
[HOTARU] For all of us as well.
[SHUGO] I'm not going
to Data Drain everyone.
The one that's going
to be Data Drained...
Will be me.
[RENA] B-Big brother!
[SHUGO] Rena...
[SHUGO] I don't want to
experience memories
like that ever again.
I know this is the best
way to save Rena.
If I'm not the hero
that can save her now...
Then I don't deserve
to exist in The World.
[KAMUI]
So, death would be better?
[SANJURO] Lunacy!
[MICHI] Is that really
such a foolish thing?
To know death and face it?
[MORTI] To know...
That is all I desire...
[BALMUNG] Shugo...
You're mistaken!
[SHUGO] Wha...?
[BALMUNG] It's no longer a
matter involving the two of you.
It's a matter that involves
the entirety of The World
[SHUGO] B-But...
[HOTARU]
Shugo, you're forgetting
the most important thing...
[SHUGO] The most
important thing?
[OHKA] That you're
not the only one
in our little group
who wants to save Rena.
[HOTARU] That's right!
[MIREILLE] Yeah, that's right...
Otherwise we wouldn't
have come this far together!
There'll be no more
giving up, for me!
[BALMUNG] We're with you,
so if you're going to use
Data Drain, use it on all of us!
That way we'll be sure to
increase the chances of success!
[SANJURO] Exactly right!
[SHUGO] Everyone...?
[HOTARU] Shugo, look out!
[KAMUI] Someone has
to get its attention.
[BALMUNG] Kamui!
[KAMUI] Hurry up
with the Data Drain!
[SANJURO] Shugo!
[SHUGO] If this fail--
No hard feelings, huh?!
[RENA] Oh... Shugo...
[SHUGO]
Data Drain.
[REKI] Balmung,
please don't screw this up.
Oscar move!!!
[MIREILLE] It worked!
Look at that!
My staff is back!
Uh?
[HOTARU] Wow Grunty!
Shugo was right...
and you got so big!
[SHUGO] Alright!
Let the fighting begin!
[SHUGO] But can we beat it...?
Just the three of
us are standing...?
[BALMUNG] I know
there's no such thing
as a monster that cannot
be defeated in combat
That's an absolute
rule in The World
[BALMUNG] Whatever the monster,
there's always
a way to kill it...
So find it's weakness...
[BALMUNG] Don't give up
until the end!
[KAMUI] Well, looks like
it's up to the newbies!
[BALMUNG] They're
our only chance...
[SHUGO] Thunder Dance!
[MIREILLE] Vak Don!
[HOTARU] Pha Repth!
[MIREILLE] Thank you! Hotaru!
[MICHI] The fools...
Why are they bullying Morti?
She and I, we just wanted
to learn about
the nature of "death"...
That's all...
[SHUGO] Our attacks
are having absolutely
no effect of that thing...
With this... could I?
Oh!
[AURA] You must use the power
of the bracelet to finish this.
[SHUGO] Eh?!
[AURA] Data Drain may
be the only way...
[SHUGO] The only way.
[AURA] Shu-Shugo...
[SHUGO] Aura...!
Oh!
[RENA] Oh!
[AURA] Data Drain
may be the only way...
When the virus has
completely infected Rena,
there will be a brief moment
before the infection
spreads to the entire area.
[AURA] If you do
that,you may be able to drain
just the virus and not Rena.
Know that the
timelag is less than
one one-thousandth of a second.
Follow your heart.
[RENA] It'll be all right.
You can do it...
Shugo.
[SHUGO] I'll get you back...
I swear!
[SHUGO] Data...
Dra-a-a-a-ain!
[RENA] Shugo!
[SHUGO] Rena!
[SHUGO] Rena...
[SHUGO] Get away from her!
[MORTI] Death to all you
Player Characters...
and Death to this world...
[Shugo
Hyper Thunder Dance!
[MICHI] No!!!
[RENA] Shugo!
[SHUGO] Rena!!
[HOTARU]
Hang on, Mireille!
[SANJURO] What's that...?
[BALMUNG] Chaos Gates...?
[SHUGO] Wh-What's that?
[MICHI] It's running now...
The final trap...
[SHUGO] What do
you mean by that?
[REKI] Five minutes until
the system goes down...
Why?
[MICHI] The trap
creates a limitless
amount of corrupted data.
It will continue to bury
The World until it
collapses on itself...
in order to destroy
any and all evidence...
[SHUGO] But why?
[KOMIYAN] This is so weird!
You're all weird!
Somehow this must be your fault!
C'mon Rena!
We have to log out, quickly!
[MICHI] All the gates in
The World are being used
to transmit the infinite
stream of destructive data...
Logout is impossible.
[OHKA] That girl is...
[KAMUI] That girl's
the fourth child...
[KAMUI] She's one
of the children
that started all of this.
[MIREILLE] But, the rumor
was that all the trouble
was caused by a
group of three boys...
[KAMUI] Yes, but
I looked into it.
It would have been quite
a feat for three of them...
but four people would've
worked much better...
[SHUGO] So did
the wandering A.I.
use this group of kids and
control what they were doing?
[MICHI] That wasn't it.
[MICHI] I met her and
she became my friend...
I know that sounds
like an odd thing to say.
I made friends with something
that was born from lingering
shreds of undeleted data.
If only she would have been able
to answer all the
questions I had for her.
I guess some things
we aren't meant to know.
[RENA] What are
you talking about...?
[MICHI] She and I had
been thinking about
the true nature of
"death" in our worlds.
[MICHI] I'd searched everywhere
I could in the real world,
but I could not find
a definitive answer...
So that's why...
[MICHI] Together, we
experimented in The World
trying to find
answers to questions
in a place where
death was common.
[MICHI] However, no
matter where we looked
we didn't make any
significant progress...
even when we went as
far as introducing an
extremely aggressive virus...
[MICHI] If there was
one thing we learned...
It was that "death"
in the real world
was just like
"deletion" here.
[RENA]
That's not right!
[SHUGO] If that's
really what you think...
[RENA]
Then why did you and Morti
try to make a world that
was like... an afterlife?
[RENA] Maybe it's because
you wanted to be certain
that there's a place
where our loved ones
would be waiting for us.
[SHUGO] I think everyone
would like to know that...
We all want to know
that there's somewhere
nice to go to after we die...
[RENA] Years ago
someone once said...
death is like parting.
[RENA] But now,
people who have been
separated by time or distance,
have a chance to
meet in The World.
I'd like to think
there's a place
where we can meet those
who have passed away
and be together again!
[SHUGO] Yeah!
[MICHI] A while ago...
I may have wanted
to believe that.
Although I don't really
understand how that could be.
She who knows
not death,
she who sacrificed
herself for me...
and is no longer
in this world...
She might have seen
that place... But,
it's already too
late... The World and everything
within it, will collapse soon.
[SHUGO] Collapse?
What about us?
[MICHI] I don't know...
Will we really die or will be in
an eternal slumber...?
Come to think of it,
years ago someone once likened
death to an eternal sleep.
[RENA] You're okay with that?
If we all die here?
[BALMUNG] It's too
soon to give up hope!
[BALMUNG] There's
still one unsolved
mystery about everything
that's happened here...
[HOTARU] What kind of mystery?
[BALMUNG] Why didn't Aura
just bring back Shugo...
Kite... by himself?
Why did she also
bring back Rena...
Black Rose...?
[SANJURO] It can't be?!
[BALMUNG] Shugo and Rena...
There must be a larger meaning
for gathering and protecting
both of them...
Maybe if they're together,
some kind of power
will be released...
[MICHI]
The Bracelet...
[SHUGO] Eh?
[MICHI] If there is such
a power to be released...
the key to it would
be the bracelet.
If there was one thing that
Morti feared the most...
it was that.
[SHUGO] This bracelet...?
[RENA]
Shugo...
[SHUGO] Rena...
[SHUGO] Now...
I think I understand...
[RENA] I do too.
[SHUGO and RENA] Whoa!
[SHUGO] Let's go Rena...
[RENA] Yeah, Shugo!
[SHUGO] Our world...
[RENA] ...is The World!
[SHUGO] We'll protect it!
[BALMUNG] Rena and Shugo...
we're counting on you!
[MIREILLE] Shugo! Rena!
[MIREILLE] Ta-dah!
I've finally gotten ahold of it!
[MIREILLE] Lookit,
lookit, loookit!
Three sets of rare silk items!
[OHKA] Yeah, but who'd be
caught dead wearing those?
[HOTARU] Hey! it's Kamui!
[MIREILLE] Ah... Greetings!
[Magi] Okay...
everyone's here right?
[KAMUI] Are we going somewhere?
[SANJURO] There appears to be
some sort of special event...
[BALMUNG] Sorry to
keep you all waiting...
[BALMUNG] Today's event is
going to be something to see.
[HOTARU] In this gonna be...
another one of Balmung's
special events?
[MIREILLE] Ew...
[REKI] Well , it'll be okay.
I made sure to check it first.
But the 2 most important
people are not here yet...
[HOTARU] It's all right.
They'll be here soon.
[MIREILLE] After all, the only
place where they can meet
is in The World since they live
so far away from each other.
[SANJURO] Here in The World that
the two of them protected.
[HOTARU] Ha!
[SHUGO] Sorry we're late!
[RENA] Yeah!
Sorry to make you wait!
[MIREILLE] They're here!
[RENA] You look great, everyone!
[HOTARU] Yes!
[KOMIYAN] Tres Bien!
[OHKA] I'm itching to fight!
[SANJURO] It's been a while,
shall we go train, Shugo?
[SHUGO] Yeah! Let's go Sanjuro!
[RENA] It's all right to train,
but don't forget about your
sister, remember?!
[SHUGO] Of course not!
We won't ever be separated
again.
The World is a place where we
can always be together,
no matter what separates us in
the real world...
[MICHI] And if your heart truly
desires it...
It's a place where you can
always meet again!
[SHUGO and RENA] The legendary
heroes are back!