[KATSUYUKI] So that's
the answer then.
[HAYATO] What is?
[KATSUYUKI] That player
that was able
to bring down our monster.
[DAISUKE] Really?
How did he do that?
[KATSUYUKI]
It was Data Drained.
[MICHI] It was Data Drained?
[HAYATO] It's the
ability to rewrite
the monster's data
and weaken it.
[MICHI] That is
some kind of power.
[KATSUYUKI]
There's only one person
in The World that has
that kind of ability...
[Katsuyuki
...and that's Kite...
[HAYATO] You mean one of
the legendary dot hackers?
[DAISUKE] That name
brings back memories.
[KATSUYUKI]
What're we gonna do?
[DAISUKE] We'll just delete our
little problem and it's bye-bye.
[HAYATO] But how?
[MICHI] How about this area?
[KATSUYUKI] Cool.
It'll be a cinch if we
can lure him out there.
Piece of cake!
[FEMALE giggling]
Catch!
[SHUGO] Woah! Isn't
the ocean fantastic!
[SHUGO] Hey! What
are you doing, man!
Ow!
[Macho PC] Sorry!
Oh, haven't we
met before...?
We must
be connected by
the red thread of fate and
destined to play together...
[Macho PC] Would you like
to form a party with me?
[SHUGO chuckles uncomfortably]
[Macho PC] Then, maybe we
could just live together?
[Macho PC laughing]
Just kidding!
[SHUGO] Just give me
back my summer...
[RENA] Hey, Shugo!
Sorry to keep you waiting!
[RENA] I bought this suit
in town at the item store.
How do I look?
[SHUGO] Uh... Great!
[MIREILLE] This is a rare
item from my secret cache.
It's a "School Swimsuit."
Whaddya think?
[MIREILLE] And Shugo,
Ohka is coming soon too!
[OHKA speaking in a sexy voice]
How do I look, Shugo?
[SHUGO sighs]
[OHKA] Sorry to
keep you waiting!
[SHUGO] Ohka!
Wolf form, huh?
[RENA] What's wrong
with you, Shugo?
[SHUGO] Oh, nevermind.
[OHKA] He was probably having
some scandalous fantasy.
[SHUGO] Oh, be quiet.
What are you
doing here, anyway?
[OHKA] Tracking you down.
[RENA and SHUGO]
Tracking us?
[RENA] Uh, Sanjuro...
[SHUGO] Sanjuro!
[SANJURO]
Rena... Shugo...
There's something
we need to talk about.
[SHUGO] Huh...?
[RENA] Um, is
everything okay?
[SANJURO] This game,
The World... is it fun?
[SHUGO] Yeah.
[RENA] Yeah, absolutely.
[SANJURO] I see...
But there is one thing
that's been bothering me.
Kids your age have so
many other things to do.
[RENA] Huh?
[SHUGO] Um...
Whattya trying to say?
[SANJURO] Too much water
drowns the miller, as they say.
If you do something in excess,
it is not good for you.
[SANJURO] You mean to make
those two quit The World?!
Was it not you who spoke that
the Twilight is approaching!
Kite's power...
No Shugo's power will
be needed in the conflict.
[BALMUNG] You're right.
This is only... a game.
[BALMUNG] The reason
users play this game
is so they can get
together and have fun.
As long as they don't
wish to be involved,
I cannot force them
to do our bidding for us.
[SANJURO] And now...?
[BALMUNG] Several players
have recently become involved
in some serious incidents...
that have become unhappy.
[BALMUNG] For some, this is
no longer just entertainment.
And we must not forget,
that many of our users are
merely children playing a game.
[RENA] I don't understand why
you're saying we have
to quit The World?!
[SANJURO] Not so long ago
a friend of mine became
addicted to this game
and sadly he's been shunning
the real world ever since
and now I'm concerned
for you two.
[RENA] We're fine though.
We know the difference
between fantasy and reality.
[SHUGO] Yeah!
[SANJURO]
Admirable words my friends,
but it may not be a bad idea
to stop playing The World
for at least a little while.
When you return,
I am sure more wondrous
discoveries will await you.
[SHUGO] But in order for me
to make those
wonderful discoveries,
I want to become stronger.
You gotta understand,
don't you, Master!
[SANJURO] Huh?
[SHUGO] Master!
[SHUGO] Master?
Teacher, maybe?
[SANJURO] Master...
Teacher...
Has a lovely ring to it...
[RENA] Well, whatever
you guys decide on,
there are still
plenty of events to clear
if we're gonna take it
easy for a while.
[SANJURO] Events?
[SHUGO] Yeah, right after
I started playing the game,
this beautiful girl in white
appeared to me
in a strange area...
And she gave me
this bracelet.
[AURA] The only one
who can save the world...
...that one is you.
[SHUGO] And then she said...
I could save
the whole, entire world.
[SANJURO] Aura!
[RENA] After all,
it looks like
we're the dot hacker
characters now.
And it looks like there
are some special events
that are connected to us.
[SHUGO]
Yeah, really cools things
that normal players don't
get a chance to experience...
like really neat monsters
that never seem to die.
[RENA] Yeah, right!
[BALMUNG] As long as they
don't wish to be involved,
I cannot force them to
do our bidding for us.
[SANJURO] If anything
out of the ordinary
happens while you're playing
I'd like you to
contact me immediately.
It doesn't matter how
trivial it may seem.
[SANJURO] That also goes for
entering unfamiliar areas.
f you sense danger,
don't access for a while.
There's no need to force
yourself to clear an event.
[RENA] But...
[Sanjuro The World is designed
to be enjoyed by all players.
It's not a place where you
should be risking your life.
[RENA] So when
all is said and
done, what was
he trying to say?
[SHUGO] Something like just
play for a few hours a day...
I guess.
[RENA] Old Sanjuro!
He's so preachy--
I bet that guy
is some kind of school
teacher in real life.
[MICHI crying]
[KATSUYUKI] Can I borrow
this for a while?
[MICHI] Give it back,
that ball is the first
item I've earned here.
[HAYATO] Finders keepers!
[DAISUKE] Well, it's ours now!
[RENA] Hey! Knock it off!
[RENA] Cut it out, you guys!
She's just a little girl!
Pick on someone else!
[SHUGO] Give 'er back the ball!
[MIREILLE] Hey, hey, hey!
[OHKA] Alright! A fight a fight!
[DAISUKE] Aw! More friends!
[KATSUYUKI] You want
the ball so bad?!
[DAISUKE] See ya 'round,
Old Hag!
[RENA] What a rude jerk;
I'm only 14 years old!
[MICHI] Did you get my ball?
[SHUGO] Yeah.
[RENA] Are you all right?
[MIREILLE]
Guys can be such wolves;
you always gotta be careful.
[OHKA] Women are
wolves actually.
[MICHI] I'm going home.
[SHUGO] Here you go.
[MICHI] Thanks a lot.
[SHUGO] Uh yeah...!
No need to thank...
[HAYATO] How did it go?
[MICHI] Piece of cake!
[DAISUKE] We did it,
we got his member address!
[KATSUYUKI] All righty!
Let's begin Operation
Delete the Dot Hackers!
[SHUGO] I'm back!
Hey, Dad? I'm home.
[SHUGO] Message?
[SHUGO] What is this?
[SHUGO] Save... Me...
[SHUGO] This is
impossible to read...
[MIREILLE] Beware the
Cursed Woodland Murderhouse.
[SHUGO] Is that
really what it said?
[MIREILLE] My corrupted text
auto decoder from my item stash
managed to successfully
translate the area name.
[RENA] Are you sure?
[MIREILLE] The text corruption
from the original
source was pretty bad,
so I wasn't able
to decode everything...
[SHUGO] But we definitely know
what area that girl is
in so we can find her...
[HOTARU] C'mon let's hurry
so we can go save her!
[OHKA] yeah,
I'm dyin' for another fight.
[SANJURO] A mail from Aura...
No explanation...
Cursed Woodland Murderhouse!
[SHUGO] This is cool...
[OHKA] It's like something's
just waiting to happen here.
[MIREILLE] I smell a rare item
just waiting to be discovered!
[HOTARU] Rena,
what's the matter?
[RENA] N-Nothing
[SANJURO] Do not let your guard
down even for a moment, Shugo
[SHUGO] I'm ready
for action, Sanjuro!
All right?
Then, let's go!
[BALMUNG] This is a brilliance
that cleanses the heart...
[REKI] Lord Balmung!
[BALMUNG] Reki...
I've completed the repairs here.
I have to go to...
[REKI] Ah, not yet,
Lord Balmung.
There are over 200
obstacle claims
that have come in
just this morning.
All the staff have given up
their day off to deal with it
and the claims just keep
pouring in from every direction!
[BALMUNG] The strange
weather in this area?
Can it be a coincidence...
Reki!
[REKI] Yes?
[BALMUNG] I'm leaving
it up to you.
There's something I must
attend to right away...
[Knight A] You are in violation
of altering the system data!
In the name of the
Cerulean Knights you
will be taken into custody!
[REKI] You have no right
to just warp into here and take
over!
Who do you think this man is?
[Knight B] Don't know.
[REKI] You seriously don't know?
[Knight B] I don't.
[REKI] This must be
some kind of joke!
[Knight B] I don't
know and don't care!
[KAMUI] Lower your swords.
This man here is
a system administrator.
[BALMUNG] Kamui...
[KAMUI] Lord Balmung...
[BALMUNG] What brings you here?
[KAMUI] The Cerulean Knights
have but a singular purpose,
to preserve the order and
peace throughout The World.
For that purpose we will go
to whatever area we choose.
[REKI] We are protecting
the order and peace
on this server, not you.
[KAMUI] Oh really...?
There's been an increase
in unstable activity
here recently, correct?
[KAMUI] Because Lord Balmung
of the Azure Sky
is too lenient with the users...
I cannot be assured this will
not grow into a larger problem.
[KAMUI] Knights!
Place an activity
monitor in this area.
Move out!
[REKI] So those were the
infamous Cerulean Knights, huh?
I've heard
they've been deleting
non-standard characters
without mercy.
[BALMUNG] Yes, yes.
Public control forces under
the direct command
of the CC Corporation.
The company's dogs...
[SHUGO] The girl is lost
somewhere inside
this old mansion...
[MIREILLE]
Rare Item. Rare Item...
[OHKA] Where are
all the monsters?
[board creaks]
[HOTARU] Are you
hungry or something?
[HOTARU] Just now
I heard your stomach growl.
[SHUGO] Oh!
[HOTARU] It appears to...
be a dining room...
[OHKA] Just a bug...
[RENA] That freaked me out.
[MIREILLE] I'm guess that you're
easily spooked, huh Rena?
[SHUGO] Come to think of it,
she used to disappear
whenever there was
a scary show on television.
Pretty funny.
Remember that, Reina?
[MIREILLE] I knew it.
[SHUGO] Don't worry, Rena!
I'm here for you!
[OHKA]
Now I'm freaked out.
[RENA] I'm fine.
I'm perfectly fine in
a place like this...
No matter how real it seems,
it's just a game.
[SHUGO] You'll be fine
in this old pace.
I'm here with you.
[RENA] Yeah, right!
I'm gonna go in there and you
just watch me not be scared.
[SHUGO] Rena!
[RENA] Knock it off!
Give me some space!
[KOMIYAN] I find it
deliciously perfect
that Rena is so
easily scared...
I'm so fortunate that I
noticed them coming here
and it was so worth it to sneak
in here ahead of time.
[KOMIYAN] Ohhh!
Such a nice situation!
[RENA] Whoa!
I'm scared!
[KOMIYAN] My Rena!
[RENA] Komiyama,
you're so wonderful!
[KOMIYAN] Tres Bi-ennnnnn!
[RENA] Hey...
Which way do I go?!
Nothing that way.
Where is everyone?
I told them just to back off,
then I thought
they'd come after me...
[RENA] I'm on my own now...
Well, I'll be fine.
I'll just remember that
this is an artificial world.
[SHUGO] Rena!
[KOMIYAN] Rena!
Incoming!
Eh?
[RENA]
D-D-Don't come any closer!
[MIREILLE] That voice came
from down this hallway I think.
[HOTARU] Rena if
you're down there say so!
[SANJURO] Do not
let your guard down.
[SANJURO]
It's dangerous for her
to be alone
in an unknown area.
Find her!
[SHUGO] Got it!
[OHKA] This time
it's a real... Monster.
[HOTARU] You did it!
[MIREILLE] Well, it looks
like they got the monsters,
but I don't see any
treasure chest for us.
[RENA]
Shugo!
Hey, Everyone!
Where did you go?
I can't tell which way is out...
[RENA] Why did
I try to act so cool.
[RENA] Oh?
[RENA] I wonder... Oh...
[RENA] Someone...
Open the door...!
[AURA] The plan
was to lure out Kite...
But the one caught in
the trap is just as good...
[AURA] Black Rose, indeed...
[MIREILLE] Aw!
We've killed them so many times
already!
[MIREILLE] Vak Don!
[OHKA] These guys definitely
aren't normal monsters!
[SANJURO] Shugo!
Leave this to us and go
find Rena immediately.
We're leaving as soon
as you find her!
[SHUGO] R-Right!
[RENA screams]
[SHUGO] Rena!
How could I...
die with just one hit?
[RENA] Help me, Shugo...
[SHUGO] Rena, don't worry.
I can heal you.
[RENA] You can't...
There's no time.
[RENA] It's one of those
monsters that just won't die...
[RENA] I'm... done...
[SHUGO] Rena... Rena!
[SHUGO] Data Drain!
[SHUGO] Rena!
[OHKA] Rena!
[MIREILLE]
I'll heal you, Rena!
[MIREILLE] Repth!
No...?!
That spell has to work!
[SHUGO] Rena!
[RENA] Oh, Shugo...
[RENA] Shugo!
[SHUGO] Rena!
[RENA] I have event information!
An outdoor hot
springs bath is open
in the area
Enraged Dragon Queen!
Hey, guys, don't worry
about looking for me.
Just enjoy your bath.
Hey, while you're at
it, pass me the soap.