[SHUGO]
Rena! Rena!
Rena!
[SHUGO] She's just gone.
How could someone just disappear
like that without a trace?
[RENA] Oh, Shugo
[SHUGO] Rena!
[RENA] Shugo!
[SHUGO] It couldn't be her...
[OHKA] It's no good.
I couldn't find
a single trace of Rena
on that side
of the mansion.
Have you had any luck?
[HOTARU] No... no sign of Rena's
ghost on this side either.
[OHKA] It's a little early
to look like you've given up.
[HOTARU] Shugo, try to
look on the bright side.
[SHUGO] What bright side?
She won't pick up the phone
back in the real world.
We can't find her
ghost anywhere in here.
Man, can someone tell me
what's going on in this place.
[OHKA] I agree, there's
nothing normal about it.
[HOTARU] Sanjuro sure
had a serious expression
when he went off to
search in that direction.
Maybe he found her?
[MIREILLE] Hey! Hey!
I think I have
an idea what's happening!
[SHUGO] Is that you,
Mireille?!
[OHKA] Do you always go around
searching under the floor?
[HOTARU]
What did you find out?
[SHUGO] Yeah!
What's going on?
[MIREILLE]
It's a special event!
[SHUGO] Eh! A special event?
[MIREILLE] That's right.
There's no other
possible explanation.
[SHUGO] Is that
part of the game?
[MIREILLE] Speaking from
my experience in The World,
I've come to the conclusion
that there's
no other thing it can be.
Just look at all the weird stuff
that's been happening
around Shugo since he got here.
[SHUGO] Well, I guess now
that you put it that way...
[OHKA] That's got to be it.
We have looked
all over for her
[HOTARU]
So I guess that means
she's gone to another area.
[MIREILLE]
So the race is on.
Let's get out of
this spooky place
and start looking for Rena.
Then we'll be the first
to clear the event
And then we'll get
some fabulous rare item!
[SHUGO] At least you could
act just a little worried
[MIREILLE]
It's a special event!
A special event!
[MIREILLE] Now, let's
put our plan in motion
to win the race
to save the missing Rena!
[MIREILLE] To start, I'll
go to the information shop
to check for any breaking
news on her whereabouts.
Everyone else
should spread out
and search for
her here in the city.
[SHUGO] Search for her here?
[MIREILLE] Let's go!
[OHKA] Alright, everyone.
Let's get going!
[HOTARU]
Where exactly are we going?
[OHKA] Into the crowd.
[SHUGO] Oh? R-Right!
[SHUGO] Since Rena is styled
after the legendary hero
character Black Rose,
someone must have seen her!
They had to of.
If she's here,
I'm gonna find her!
All right, I'm coming, Rena!
A Player Character
styled after Black Rose.
There's someone like that?
[PC #4] Sorry I don't know.
[PC #7 Male Blade]
I can't say.
[KOMIYAN] Tres Bien!
There's Kunisaki!
So my beloved
Rena must be close at hand!
[KOMIYAN]
Oh Rena!
[SHUGO]
We've looked everywhere!
[FEMALE BLADE] Black Rose?
I think she was
in the park earlier.
[SHUGO] Let's go!
Thank you for your help.
[FEMALE BLADE] I'd heard people
talk about a Player Character
that looked just like
Black Rose here in The World
but I thought
it was just a rumor.
[SHUGO] Wha...?
Rena could be
anywhere in this place?
So This was the last
place she was seen?
[HOTARU] Y'know, a
thought just occurred to me
[SHUGO] What kind of thought?
[HOTARU] I thought that...
[OHKA] You thought what?
[HOTARU] ...we could
use little Grunty.
[SHUGO] Your Grunty?
[HOTARU] I was thinking of
giving the Grunty
Rena's scent to search for.
[OHKA] I wasn't aware that a
Grunty could do that.
[HOTARU] Oh, he can!
Because, he's grown
so much lately.
[SHUGO] I get it, since
Grunties are animals,
they must have a better
sense of smell than we do.
[SHUGO] Alright,
go forth, Grunty!
Now is the time you prove
your usefulness to us!
We're ready for your
nose to lead us to Rena!
[SHUGO] Wake up!
[SHUGO] How useless!
We need a real tracker.
[SHUGO] Hey! I've got it.
We could use man's best friend
to help us sniff
out Rena's trail!
[OHKA] A werewolf is not a dog!
[BALMUNG] Why are you late?
As I recall, you were
the one who contacted me.
[SANJURO] I'm sorry.
There was something
I was looking into.
[BALMUNG] Looking into?
That's quite unlike you.
[SANJURO] I had
no choice this time.
[BALMUNG] So, why did you call?
[SANJURO] Black Rose--
Rena has disappeared.
[SANJURO] What concerns me
is when she was killed by Death,
she disappeared without
becoming a ghost.
[REKI] There's no way!
That can't happen
[BALMUNG] Sanjuro...
[BALMUNG] There is one thing
that I am certain of...
[SHUGO] She's not here anywhere?
[HOTARU] No one just vanishes.
[SHUGO] Right!
This calls for an
all-area search!
[HOTARU] Rena, where are you?
[SHUGO] Rena!
[SHUGO] Rena?
[SHUGO] Rena...
But if I remember...
Rena used to get
lost all the time.
[SHUGO] Rena!
Rena!
[RENA] Shugo!
[RENA] Hey Shugo?
[SHUGO] Eh? Yeah?
[RENA] Nothing.
Just say something funny.
Oh, okay
Um...
A cute puppy fell in the river.
Whoops!
Splash!
[RENA] Now, that's my
silly brother!
[RENA] Big brother!
Big Brother?
Big Brother.
Just say something funny okay?
[SHUGO] Rena!
[OHKA] Poor Shugo.
[HOTARU] He's really pouring his
heart out to find his sister.
[DAISUKE] Found him!
[Michi] There's no mistake,
it's Kite, alright.
He's searching here
of all places?
[KATUYUKI] Because of a slight
miscalculation last time,
we killed Black Rose
instead of Kite.
[Michi] This is good
Kite's lost his best friend
so his heart is wide open.
That'll make it easy for us.
[HAYATO] Just leave it up to
me
and it'll go
smoothly this time.
[DAISUKE] So, do you have a
plan to get him for sure?
[HAYATO] Oh yeah.
He'll be completely exposed and
deletable this time around.
It'll happen so fast he won't
even have time to Data Drain.
[MIREILLE] I see
So , there was no sign
of her trail anywhere.
Nothing.
What about you, Mireille?
[MIREILLE] Empty handed.
I couldn't find any particular
event information,
and no one I chatted
with had seen Rena.
[OHKA] Ah!
So I guess this isn't some
kind of event after all.
[SHUGO] Then...
where's Rena?
[MIREILLE] Ah, did
anyone think
that maybe she
just logged out?
[OHKA] Or she might
have just gotten scared
or hopelessly lost.
[HOTARU] And that would be okay.
Even if you die in the game,
it's not like you die
in the real world.
[OHKA] How is it you can talk
about expiring
with a big smile
on your face?
[HOTARU] Expiring...
it's not that hot in
here, is it?
[OHKA] Huh?
[MIREILLE] Anyway,
this is so strange.
I thought for sure this was all
some kind of event.
[SHUGO] Now I'm worried.
What could've happened to her?
[SHUGO] Eh?
[MIREILLE] What's up?
[HOTARU] What's wrong Shugo?
Did you hear something?
[SHUGO] New mail
[MIREILLE] It's got
to be from Rena!
Check it out quick!
[SHUGO] It says the
sender is unknown.
[HOTARU] Unknown?
[OHKA] So, does it say
anything worthwhile?
[SHUGO] It's a pretty
short message.
All it says is "Enraged
Dragon Queen."
[MIREILLE] That's got to
be an area name!
I'm sure of it
[MIREILLE] So it was a
special event after all!
[SHUGO] Huh? You think so?
[OHKA] A friend suddenly goes
missing
then a mail with no known sender
comes in
and all it contains is a
mysterious area name be careful.
[HOTARU] In other words
[MIREILLE] It's got to be
something really special
that ordinary players can't
see...
the ultimate special event and
it's all for us to discover!
Sounds like fun!
[SHUGO] If I go there do you
think Rena will
[MIREILLE] be waiting for you
within a dramatic Event!
[SHUGO] I get it!
After all, I did
win the costume
of Kite the Legendary
Hero right?
So it only makes sense
that a dramatic meeting,
worthy of such a hero,
is waiting with Rena
as the ultimate reward!
Let's go get her!
[HOTARU] Okay, let's go!
It's off to "Raging Drag Queen!"
[SHUGO] Agrh!
It looks like none of us packed
very well for the cold weather
[MIREILLE] Ahh!
Ohka!
You're the only one with a fur
coat, how unfair!
[OHKA] Stop it! Stop it!
[MIREILLE] How unfair!
[SHUGO] Whoa it's cold!
[HOTARU] I just feel sorry for
Rena
To be stuck all alone in
such a cold place like this
[SHUGO] Rena...
[SHUGO] It-It'll be all right
She can be pretty good
at taking care of herself
when she needs to.
[SHUGO] Huh?
[SHUGO] Huh? This is odd
[MIREILLE] What, what?
[SHUGO] It's all steamy so I
can't really tell.
[OHKA] If it's some kind of a
monster, just leave it to me.
[MIREILLE] Hurry up, let's go!
[SHUGO] A hot spring?
What the heck is
this doing here?
[HOTARU] This is a Hot spring?
[MIREILLE] Lucky us!
Hey hey, what are
we waiting for?
When you're cold,
there's nothing like
a steaming hot bath!
[SHUGO] You guys, don't forget!
We're looking for Rena in
this area, don't forget.
This isn't the time to go
jumping into a hot tub!
[MIREILLE] Why not?
We're probably the
only ones in The World
lucky enough to
enjoy a Hot Spring!
How can we pass up a rare
opportunity like this one!
[SHUGO] Easy, just keep walking.
[MIREILLE] I wonder if
there's a possibility
that Shugo is embarrassed?
[SHUGO] N-No way!
It's just not the time
for any of us
to be getting into hot water.
[OHKA] No worries...
...we wouldn't let you
get in over your head.
[MIREILLE] Aaaah!
Now that's what I call
a hot hot spring!
I feel like my heart and soul
have been cleansed.
[HOTARU] Cleanse your heart?
How would you do
something like that?
Do you use shampoo?
Hotaru, what planet
are you from anyway?
[MIREILLE] Shugo!
What are you doing
way over there?!
It's not like we're actually
in some kind of co-ed hot tub!
Come on!
Oh, yeah, I guess you're right.
A hero should never be afraid
to take it easy once in a while!
[MIREILLE]
C'mon and join us!
Don't make us send Ohka
over there to fetch you.
[OHKA] You wouldn't want that...
[SHUGO] Whoa!
O-Ohka! Is that you?
What the heck are you doing?!
Hey, Shugo, what're you
doing with that Grunty?
Hey Grunty what are
you doing over there?
That Grunty sure seems
to like Shugo a lot.
[OHKA] They make a cute pair.
[SHUGO] Rena!
[RENA] Hi Shugo.
[SHUGO] W-Where were
you all this time?
[RENA] Sorry I worried you.
I'm okay!
[SHUGO] We looked for
you all over the place.
[RENA] I believed in you.
I knew...
...that you would
come for me, Shugo.
[SHUGO] Uh?
[RENA] I knew you would
come to find me for sure.
[SHUGO] Ah!
W-Wait Rena!
I got the point--
I got the point!
[OHKA] This is a nice
place for a reunion
[MIREILLE] You would never think
they were brother and sister
with a serious hug like that.
[HOTARU] What a beautiful sight.
[OHKA] Well, looks like our
search is finally over.
[RENA] I'm so glad
I waited for you
[RENA] I've been
waiting all this time
for you to come to
find me, Shugo.
[SHUGO] You're not Rena.
Who are you?
[RENA] What are
you talking about?
I'm Rena.
[SHUGO] No you're not.
[RENA] But, Shugo...
[SHUGO] I mean Rena would
never say things like that.
No way Rena would just sit
around all day and do nothing!
[RENA] Stop it, Shugo.
Stop it, Shugo!
[SHUGO] I would
know if you were Rena
'cause Rena is--
[RENA] Why?
Why won't you believe me?
Why Shugo?
Get ready, Shugo!
[MIREILLE] The hot
springs are gone!
[OHKA] But how could
they... an illusion?
[HOT SPRINGS GEEZER]
Give your sister a little hug!
[MIREILLE] GiRai Don!
[SHUGO] Next time you're
thinking about saving me,
try not to kill me okay?
[MIREILLE] Don't be
so fussy about it
or there might not
be a next time.
Now get dressed or
you'll catch a cold.
[OHKA] It's one of those
modified monsters!
[OHKA] What's going on?
[MIREILLE] Ah!
That can't be good!
[HOT SPRINGS GEEZER]
Don't run away!
Stop and fight!
[SHUGO] That's it!
You can't insult my sister
by having her turn into a
monster like you!
[HOT SPRINGS GEEZER]
Farewell Big Brother!
[SHUGO] I'll be the
one saying farewell!
No one messes
with my sister!
Data Drain!
[Long Lived] Oh, it
looks like I'm just
a bit overdone.
Oh, what a world...
what a world!
[OHKA] So this wasn't
an event after all.
I wonder who that mail
could have been from?
[MIREILLE] I wonder...
M-Maybe this is
some kind of event,
only it's just the first part.
[SHUGO] Ah! Oh, it's you.
[BALMUNG] I understand
that Rena has disappeared.
[SHUGO] What do
you know about it?
Did you guys set
this special event up?
[BALMUNG] You can be assured
that we didn't take Rena,
but there are a few things
that you need to know.
Shugo, all of this
seems to be related
to the contest
you and you sister won,
and the Kite and Black Rose
characters you now resemble.
[REKI] That contest
was not official
and it was not run
by the CC Corporation.
It's something
that was contrived
outside of official channels.
[SHUGO] What does
that mean exactly?
And how do you know
so much about it?
[REKI]
Because Balmung and I
are System Administrators
for the CC Corporation.
[SHUGO]
System Administrators?
[MIREILLE]
Lord Balmung, too?
[BALMUNG] Shugo, this
is not a special event.
It's a very serious incident!
[SHUGO] Hello? Mom?!
[SHUGO gasps]
What happened to her?!
[SHUGO] Rena!
[RENA] I have information
for inquiring minds!
Everyone's after Shugo,
and The Heavy Blade named
Rena has fallen into a coma.
Huh?
I did?
I'm in trouble!
Hurry up, Shugo!