[DOCTOR]
So tell me again,
How many people does this make?
[DOCTOR B] Well, I don't
have the latest count, Doctor.
The talk is that the entire
CC Corporation staff fell
mysteriously ill.
[DOCTOR] And all of this
is because of that game?
[DOCTOR B]
Well, the research team
hasn't found anything
conclusive yet, I'm afraid.
[DOCTOR]
All these comatose people,
and they were all
playing that game?
That has to have
raised some suspicions.
[DOCTOR B]
Yeah, you do have a point.
[DOCTOR]
Games...
The effect of virtual
reality on the subconscious
has been the subject of
quite a bit of analysis
in various research
circles, but...
...these cases are particularly
difficult to connect.
[DOCTOR B]
You're right.
[EXECUTIVE] That is the final
decision of the committee.
Reki, I will leave
the rest to you.
[REKI]
Yes, sir.
[EXECUTIVE]
As you no doubt know,
Kamui followed Balmung
and is no longer assigned.
And with Magi in a coma,
You are the only qualified
employee remaining.
Yes. Thank you, sir.
I understand.
[EXECUTIVE] It is the earnest
desire of this company
that an end be
put to this affair.
We are reporting to the
media that the true cause
of the incident was
no more than a prank
started by three
juvenile miscreants.
So there won't be a
public announcement
about that wandering A.I.?
[EXECUTIVE] We are
leaving that up to you.
Reki, you are the
only qualified person
to speak to the
technical specifics.
Understood. It's just...
...that the incident
was so much more
than just an incident.
[EXECUTIVE]
Of course.
I will approve the usage
of System Management
Clause three eighteen.
Regarding investigation of the
incident within the system,
your authority over the matter
is now entirely unrestricted.
Hey, hey!
Did you read the paper?
Yeah, not a word of it
came out in the press today.
Not the truth about the incident
or even a hint about
what had happened.
I hear it's even worse
inside the CC Corporation.
Even if something did happen,
they're saying
it's not their fault.
Well, thanks to those guys,
we can all still be in The World
and figure it out together.
It's certainly a warm
tropic on the boards.
Uh, I think you mean
it's a hot topic.
Jeez, no one knows the truth
about what really happened,
so they're saying
anything they want
out there on the boards.
I heard that someone wrote
that the Cerulean Knights
were all blasted
by some cursed item.
Or that they figured out
how to cast spells
in the real world.
Or that they all came
down with food poisoning.
Or that they were
somehow all hypnotized.
[OHKA] You guys have way too
much free time, don't you?
[MIREILLE]
What do you mean?
[SHUGO]
Rena...
[REKI]
Well-qualified, he calls me.
Why should I have to deal
with a mountain of paperwork
and press conferences
and behind-the-scenes
construction projects
and golf business trips and
all the telephone complaints?
And here I am, caught
between two worlds.
[slapping noise]
[SANJURO] The World is
much more comfortable
than what reality
has to offer, huh?
It doesn't feel
that way right now.
[SANJURO] What are you
plotting now, Reki?
[REKI] Huh?
You betrayed Balmung,
then you made Kamui
lose her position.
And most recently, you
leaked information to us.
Those aren't the
things one would expect
from a loyal person.
Hey, wait, it's like
you're trying to paint me
as some kind of bad guy
in all that's happened.
So then what's your point?
You're not doing all of this
just so you can take
Balmung's position, are you?
It didn't take me
long to realize
that the job of
System Administrator
is a tough one, even for
someone like Balmung.
[SANJURO]
So it is true!
No, Sanjuro.
I'd thank you for overestimating
me, but I'm no big shot,
let alone qualified enough
to be an administrator.
So for now, that is one job
I have no desire to pursue.
[REKI]
Well, then.
Strange young man.
Okay! Let's go!
Let's go where?
Well, isn't it obvious?
We're going to find Rena!
[MIREILLE] Shugo, it
hasn't been that long
since our last attempt.
But we're so close!
That wandering A.I.
can destroy an entire area
right underneath our feet.
We have to be careful not to end
up like those Cerulean Knights.
So what do you
think we should do?
[SANJURO] First of all,
we must be level-headed.
From now on, we
can't just rush forward
without first using our heads.
[SHUGO] But we're
running out of time!
I understand.
But a wandering A.I.
is our enemy now.
Um...
I've been wondering
about this for a while.
What is a wandering A.I.?
It's unused
non-player character data
that learned its
own consciousness.
[OHKA] I can't believe
a non-player character
could have that much power.
You may not believe it,
but it's happened.
Then are you saying
we give up on Rena?
[SANJURO] No!
That's not it at all!
It's just...
We saw her.
[RENA]
Shugo, wait!
[SHUGO]
Rena?
[RENA]
Shugo!
[SHUGO]
Rena!
[RENA]
Shugo!
But then...
I couldn't...
I couldn't do
anything to help her.
But hey!
We do have the bracelet, right?
With this thing,
we can do anything!
Not we.
You are the only one
who controls the bracelet.
There are no second
chances anymore.
Don't forget that there
are lives at stake here.
Let's think all
of this through
and meet again tomorrow
to decide our path.
Don't forget to get some rest.
So many of them.
[RENA]
My friends.
They must have come
searching for me.
I won't give up until I see
every one of them again.
Shugo.
[SHUGO]
Rena!
You're healthy
and happy now.
And we have Shugo
to thank for all of that.
Isn't that right, Grunty?
Ha!
You're my brother
Shugo, right?
Whoa!
Could you be...
...Rena?
My little twin sister?
Rena? Is it you?
Bingo!
It's sure been
awhile, big brother.
And it's our first time
meeting in character.
I'm Rena the Heavy Blade!
Nice to meet you.
[SHUGO]
Rena.
I swear,
even if I have to do it alone...
Huh?
[SANJURO]
Took you long enough.
Sanjuro. You're here.
For a student to get
up later than his master--
no excuse.
[SANJURO]
What are you doing?
You can't train
just by standing there.
All right!
[OHKA] Just the two of you,
off to some secret training?
If you want to level up,
you can't just go out
and fight your everyday
monsters, you know.
[GRUNTY squeaking]
He says...
...he wants to see
Rena again, too.
[MIREILLE] How rude, making a
lady wait here all by herself.
Mireille?
I want to see what
kind of ultra-rare items
we can find in
those strange servers,
otherwise I'll never finish.
Mireille...
[MIREILLE] Besides, if The
World becomes unusable to us,
then all the rare items I've
collected will go to waste.
Once we start this adventure,
you know we can't turn back.
Of course!
I have no hang-ups.
You know me. I'm
in 'til the end.
And I bought a lot of
medicine to heal us.
Thanks everyone. So much.
All right! Let's go!
[ALL]
Yeah!
Transcendence... leads...
to... knowledge...
[BALMUNG]
Here.
Two-to-three pawn,
and then five-to-six the bishop.
I can't win.
[REKI]
But who did you lose to?
Huh?
Hey again.
How come you logged
into The World,
then came all the way out
here just to play shogi?
Especially alone.
Haven't you interfered enough?
I'm just a regular player now,
so why don't you leave?
You're acting like a regular
player, that's for sure.
[BALMUNG] Why did you
come all the way out here?
Maybe to make fun of you.
[REKI]
That would be a lie, though.
Can I...
...talk to you about the past?
I was wondering
about the differences
between then and now?
What do you mean?
Must've been amazing fighting
side-by-side with Kite.
Or maybe it really is better
as an ex-administrator,
sulking all alone
out here in the woods.
Back then, you were
just a regular player
at the time of the first
Twilight, weren't you?
Yes, that's correct.
Reki, I understand.
Thank you!
[REKI] Balmung,
take this with you.
A master key card?
Reki!
[BALMUNG yelling]
Lord Balmung,
teleporting would be
much faster than running.
The Capitol of Illusion.
Nebel Mond.
Good plan.
Now that we're at the
private sector's Root Town,
we won't have to waste
time hacking every gate
we want to use.
That area with the
wandering A.I.
is connected to Nebel Mond.
We don't have much time,
but if we keep
searching this server...
...we'll find Rena.
A town with no people?
It's too quiet.
This place
doesn't feel right.
[HOTARU] As long as there
are no monsters, it's fine.
From this point on,
it would be best to assume that
common sense no longer applies.
--Whoa!
[SANJURO]
That's impossible!
A monster hunting
in the Root Town?
[RENA] I've walked
all over this place,
but the only landmark seems
to be the dungeon's entrance.
I guess this area must
still be under construction.
The data isn't complete,
so it isn't stable.
That's why I managed
to see Shugo fighting
in that other area.
We were so close.
Shugo.
[RENA]
I give up.
No matter which way I go,
I end up back
in this same place.
Aura...?
[RENA]
No. It's not her.
Who are you?
How did you find this place?
What is this?
[A.I.]
Death.
Death?
In order for me to
transcend death,
it is important that
I first understand it.
[RENA]
I don't get it.
I've been...
...thinking about
death for a while.
Thinking...
Data... Drain!
What?!
It split!
[MIREILLE]
How could it...
That thing's got
some kind of protection
against the Data Drain!
It can't be!
Patience, Shugo!
Another chance will come!
I've still got some
magic left in me.
I'm not exhausted yet!
You can just leave the
healing to me, everyone!
C'mon, guys!
[OHKA]
Shugo, here it comes!
[yelling]
Gi Gan Don!
[SANJURO] Slashing at it
has no effect at all!
How can our physical
attacks be no good?
Somehow we have
to put a stop
to that thing's splitting power.
I'm goin' in!
Shugo! Stop!
Stay back!
Shugo!
The old tactics won't
defeat it, Sanjuro, my friend.
Lord Balmung!
[BALMUNG] You have to fight
these things as a team.
Quickly! Rally
to a new position!
Everyone follow me!
Uh, hey...
[MONSTER roaring]
Sanjuro, Ohka, Let's go!
Mireille! Now!
LaRue Zot!
Shugo, go now!
Huh?
Don't let this
chance slip by!
Got it!
Data... Drain!
[MONSTER squeaking]
Rena...
[A.I.]
I see.
They defeated it.
Yes. Understood.
[A.I.]
I must go.
You--You have to go where?
I must transcend death.
Wait a minute!
Please wait!
Thanks, Balmung.
Y'know, if you were
planning on showing up,
you could have dropped
in a little bit sooner.
Well, I couldn't let
you guys have all the fun.
I don't think
now is the time
for us to begin celebrating.
Something's coming.
It's her again!
The Wandering A.I..
I am known by
the name of Morti.
[RENA]
This is no event.
What is this hand of evil
that creeps towards us?
What is Morti?
What time is it?
But I'm sure Shugo can do it!
C'mon, Big Brother!
I believe in you!