[CHUTA]
You...
You're still alive.
Gucchi!
[DOLUGH]
Chuta, are you okay?
Gucchi?
I'll never forget that day...
...when you killed us...
by pushing us off that cliff.
[CHUTA]
You guys, I've got a great idea.
Let's make this
field trip awesome.
Let's go climb to the
top of Mount Taketori!
Sounds cool!
That does sound fun!
I'm not sure we should
go off on our own.
Oh, we'll be fine!
Besides, we got
some time to kill!
[CHUTA]
Didn't you hear me, before?
There's nothing to worry
about! It's a safe trail!
Are you talkin'
to yourself again?
[CHUTA]
Uh!
Yeah, you got me!
[GUCCHI, MICHIYO,
MATSUTARO scream]
You guys, the cliff!
It's falling!
I can't hold them!
Chuta, help!
Just hold on!
I'm coming back down!
What?
Oh. Okay! The rock
on the right, got it!
[MICHIYO yelps]
[gasps]
[ALL screaming]
[GUCCHI]
Just think,
Michiyo and Matsutaro
would still be alive.
If only you had stayed up there,
rather than come down in
a sad attempt to help us.
Instead, your weight
destroyed the ledge.
And we all fell to our doom.
[DOLUGH]
Calm down, Chuta!
[CHUTA]
He's right. Calm down.
Now's your chance. Say what
you've always wanted to say.
Gucchi! I'm sorry!
Huh? You know damn well
"sorry"'s not enough!
You fool! You have no idea
what hell I went through!
I crashed to the ground,
barely conscious.
Then the rocks tumbled in.
I got to hear all my bones
that weren't yet broken shatter!
I realized I was going to die.
But suddenly, the darkness
closing in around me
was replaced by a bright light.
And through a miracle
of alien science,
they brought me back to life.
Who's "they"?
[DOLUGH]
Someone's coming!
That was a little steeper
than I was expecting!
Oh! 'Scuse me!
Would you mind taking
our picture, son?
Don't you dare interrupt us!
[DOLUGH]
Chuta, look!
[gasps]
[CHUTA]
No.
No! They didn't do
anything, Gucchi!
[GUCCHI] I did what I had
to do. What I wanted to do.
The Gucchi you knew as
a kid is dead and gone.
The mark of DeMille!
So that means...
[GUCCHI]
Yes.
They are the ones who brought me
back to life, so I joined them.
In turn, they've made me captain
of my very own spaceship.
[CHUTA]
No. It can't be!
My mission is to analyze
any Earth defenses
that are a hurdle to DeMille's
plans for conquest.
This means finding out the
strength of elDLIVE here.
I knew the local bureau had
Space Police undercover
at Shirobori Middle School.
But I didn't know
who they were yet.
So I sent in two grunts to
find the elDLIVE members
by using a sleep-inducing SPH.
So that was all
part of your plan.
Or should I say, DeMille's plan.
[GUCCHI] Yeah, but the
biggest surprise was on me,
learning that you're in elDLIVE.
Although, you do give
me the chance now
to accomplish my
secondary objective.
What's that?
To steal the
Monitalien from you.
You can't! He's a part of me!
[DOLUGH gasps]
Ah. Hi there, fella.
Within that small Monitalien
is undiscovered technology
from the ancient
planet Griffith.
It's value is immeasurable.
It's impossible to remove him!
You can't just pull him out!
That's only true
if you're alive.
Don't worry. I'm not
gonna kill you, Chuta.
A dead host is a problem for
even mature Monitaliens.
It causes them to lose
all accumulated data.
[CHUTA gasps]
But with DeMille's tech,
I can separate you two.
While you're still
alive and well.
I don't wanna get cut, Chuta!
Well, I don't wanna
get cut, either!
Boys.
[TRANSFER STUDENT A]
Aye-aye!
[TRANSFER STUDENT B]
Captain!
Oh, no! Misuzu and Chips!
Considering that
we're old friends,
if you hand over the
Monitalien without a fuss,
I'll give your
friends back to you.
I'll even forgive
you for throwing me
off the side of Mount Taketori.
I still know you
quite well, Chuta.
You've blamed yourself for that
day ever since, haven't you?
Even though I'm the
one who was wronged,
I'm willing to let it go.
You won't have to carry
that guilt anymore.
All that pain gone.
All the pain? Gone?
Chuta! I'm starting
to fade away!
If giving him up will help you
finally forgive me, then--
[DOLUGH]
Chuta!
[CHUTA] I just want to
put it all behind me!
No, Chuta!
[GUCCHI] Give me the
Monitalien from your chest
and I will take the weight
off your shoulders.
The past will be erased.
The pain... gone.
Chuta! I want to exist with you!
Just shut up!
All I have to do
is give you away
and everything that's happened,
the hardships and
the pain, all gone.
All gone!
Chuta.
[CHUTA]
All gone. All gone.
I'm assuming that you've
finally made a decision.
[CHUTA]
Yeah.
[GUCCHI]
Heh.
I don't need to erase my past.
Because, Gucchi...
...I have precious
memories there, too.
[gasps]
[CHUTA]
And if Dolugh stays with me,
I can beat bad guys like you.
So yeah, I've decided!
He stays with me!
[ALL gasp]
Thank you for this, Gucchi.
If you hadn't come
back to Earth,
I'd never be able to
say what I just did.
[GUCCHI]
You idiot!
And I'm gonna stop you.
Because I'm a Space Cop!
Damn you!
[CHUTA] Guchhi, surrender
and let the hostages go!
No, you give up!
Or I'll rip her in half!
Dolugh. think you can
you destroy that guy
without hurting Sonokata?
Not from this far away I can't.
Hey, wait a second! What's that
falling out of her pocket?
[CHUTA gasps]
Red wrapper? Is that--?
[DOLUGH] That's the wrapper for
the antidote to the sleep-SPH.
[CHUTA clears throat]
The three of you have
the right to remain silent.
Anything you say can and
will be used against you
in a galactic court of law.
Also, in elDLIVE
detention centers,
you can choose from Japanese
or Western meal plans.
All right, that's
enough. Give it!
[CHUTA]
You'd know what I meant, huh?
The Western entrée is steak.
Japanese is... the duck!
Now please disappear forever!
SPH. The D-blade.
What?
He's good.
[laughing]
[chuckles]
I'd say they're evenly matched!
Then let's help her!
No, don't! You'll
just get in the way!
[GUCCHI]
Yeah, she's right.
Nothing good can ever happen
when Chuta Kokonose
tries to help people.
[yells]
Sonokata!
[GUCCHI]
Whether it's your friends
falling off that cliff as kids,
or this girl lying here
today, one thing is clear.
Chuta, these deaths
are your fault.
Gucchi, no!
[GUCCHI]
You had your chance and blew it.
[CHUTA]
Face me! Coward!
[GUCCHI]
This is the end of you.
[CHUTA]
Gucchi!
[DOLUGH]
Sympathy!
[CHUTA gasps]
[GUCCHI chuckles]
You may be a Space Cop,
but you're still the same guy.
You just can't leave your
friends alone, can you?
I'm... sorry.
[GUCCHI]
Now we can talk for real.
Huh?
[GUCCHI] Your blast
destroyed the recorder
that DeMille implants
in all their personnel
to keep tabs on them.
What?
[GUCCHI]
You even took out my two guys.
This is the first
time in a long time
DeMille's not monitoring me.
Oh, and don't worry, Chuta.
Those hikers aren't
actually dead.
What you thought was a bomb
just knocks them unconscious
and covers them with black soot.
It's a little trick
I've been doing
that DeMille hasn't
caught onto yet.
You're a good guy?
[GUCCHI laughs]
[GUCCHI]
Guess so.
And when you refused that
deal I offered earlier--
y'know, for the Monitalien--
it made me happy.
Like, that's my Chuta.
The same buddy I had back
when I was a little kid.
Gucchi! You really are you!
You guys love each
other, don't you?
What? We're just friends!
Wait, so all those
times as kids,
when you were
talking to yourself,
it was really to this guy?
Pretty weird, huh?
Found out recently.
'S not that funny
There is one other big
thing I need to tell you.
[CHUTA]
Hm?
Michiyo and Matsutaro.
They still have to be
alive somewhere.
What? You're serious?
Of course I am!
I survived. Why couldn't they?
That's why I'm gonna
stay with DeMille
for as long as I can fool them.
I'll use them,
and you use elDLIVE, and we'll
find Michiyo and Matsutaro.
Okay, yeah! Great idea!
[GUCCHI]
I know, righ--? Uh!
Are you okay?
[GUCCHI]
No, I got stabbed!
Sorry. Once again,
it's my fault.
You know the fall
was just an accident.
The edge of cliff had
already started crumbling
before you ever set foot on it.
The hardest part about
this whole thing,
was knowing this entire time
you were blaming yourself
for what happened.
You've got the biggest
heart there is.
Thanks, pal.
[CHUTA yelps]
No, wait!
You're in the way!
Don't tell anyone what I said!
It's better if they all
think we're enemies!
But wait, since you failed
your mission down here,
won't they kill you?
I'm not that easy to replace.
I am a captain, y'know.
Speaking of, you should be
worrying about your own ship.
I won't hold back.
If my mom's ever
guilted you, I'm sorry!
You're lucky to be alive.
Next time, move.
[yelps]
Right. Sorry.
Chuta! Gucchi's gonna
attack the Bureau!
That's right. Sonokata!
Let's warn them!
[CHUTA] I get using fireworks
when the radio's out,
but how do they see
these from space?
[DOLUGH]
Stinky! Stinky...
[MISUZU] They're special
fireworks that contain SPH,
so they appear on the scanners.
Can we get around the jamming?
Almost there, Chief!
[MELIES]
Chief!
I've detected a weak SPH marker
in the atmosphere over Japan!
That's Sonokata!
Unscrambling.
"Warning! DeMille is going
to attack the Bureau!"
[LAINE]
Understood.
All right! Bridge,
prepare for battle!
Room Chief Magnoli!
SPH barrier up!
I need full power!
[MAGNOLI]
Yoyosa!
What's wrong?
Explosive shockwave, Chief!
Harry!
Jamming Nullification
Wave is ready, Chief.
Engage!
Huh? The radar's
back online, Chief!
[RIGGS] They've surrounded
us with space mines!
[LAINE]
What?
Shoot them down!
[RIGGS]
Yoyosa!
[CREW A] This is traffic
division! We got a hull breach!
[CREW B]
Engine status!
[CREW C]
Stable for now!
[MCCLANE] The mines are too
fast for our lasers, Chief!
Magnoli, where's
that SPH Barrier?
At full-strength now.
[LAINE]
Put it up!
[MAGNOLI] All right,
space moss, you're up!
Go out and spit as much Barrier
SPH as you can, ribbit!
[MAGNOLI] SPH Barrier forming,
Chief! Ribbit!
Welcome back, shero!
Update now!
The DeMille ship's attacking
us with space mines!
[GUCCHI] It's better if they
all think we're enemies!
[CHUTA] Yeah, but can't you
pull your punches a little bit?
It's no use!
There're too many
mines to track!
It's your move now,
elDLIVE Captain.
What's wrong, Chuta?
The little space mines,
they seem so familiar.
That swarm of
targets from training!
Yeah! Right!
Chief, can we talk?
Hey! Glad you're back!
I know how to stop the mines!
[TONTO chuckles]
[TONTO]
You think up some crazy things.
[CHUTA] The mines reminded me
of our training the other day.
Just do your
fly-swatting moves again
and I'm sure we
can take 'em out!
Well, I'll do my best!
Chief, I'm ready to go!
[LAINE]
Copy that!
[TONTO] Connection from paw
pads to laser cannons is live.
Targeting hologram deployed.
This space ship is
now one with my body.
And the cannons one with me!
Take this!
Meow!
Meow-meow-meow-meow-meow-meow!
Wow. Nice counter strike.
Now watch me.
[gasps]
The mines moved out
of the lasers range!
This is Tonto in the cannon pod!
Please turn the bow of
the ship 60 degrees port!
[RIGGS] Roger! Turning
bow 60 degrees port!
No, wait! Don't move it!
What's wrong?
Fire the elmaser cannons!
Spread 'em out wide as you can!
Yoyosa!
Harry! The spot 30
degrees from starboard,
is it optimal for hitting
Japan with SPH?
If so, I want you to target it.
I think that's
where they're hiding.
But, Chief, I'm not reading
anything at that position!
[LAINE] I know she's there.
Elmaser cannon aim.
And fire!
[HARRY]
There it is!
[RIGGS]
DeMille ship, dead ahead!
Hey there.
[RIGGS]
I see what DeMille's plan was.
They wanted us to turn
left the whole time
and were usin' the mines
to draw us that way.
Had we turned like they wanted
us to, we'd be a big, fat target
for their main battle cannons.
So by putting himself
in their shoes,
the Chief found
their exact position.
And by guessing the
optimal spot in space
from which to jam our
communications and SPH radar,
the Chief was able to confirm
that DeMille's using a
new weapon against us.
Yeah, I don't get it,
but it sure sounds amazing.
[CREWMEMBER A]
Our stealth dome is down!
They've got a straight
line of attack!
[GUCCHI]
Well, well, well.
Their captain know a thing
or two about battles.
It's time we fall back.
[CREWMEMBER B]
What that? Just give up?
Calm down. We got the
data we came for.
You found yourself a
good Bureau, Chuta.
We'll see each other soon.
DeMille ship entering warpspeed!
They are off our radar.
All mines de-activated.
That was a good fight, Chief.
But too bad they got away.
Yeah.
[ALL cheering]
Wow. You had me
scared there, Gucchi.
You had me worried back there,
but I guess I'm just lucky.
Huh?
I'm alive 'cause you
wouldn't hand me over.
Well, it's not just luck.
What is it?
More like friendship?
[CHUTA]
When Gucchi threatened us,
I looked in Dolugh's
eyes and I felt
this sense of connection
between us.
[GUCCHI'S MOM]
You're Chuta Kokonose, right?
[CHUTA]
Hm?
Hi, Mrs. Mizoguchi.
It's been a while, ma'am.
I... was just leaving.
[GUCCHI'S MOM]
No, wait.
Chuta, stay.
You were just a little boy.
I never should've blamed
you for what happened.
I hope you can forgive
me. I'm sorry.
I remember about a month
before that field trip,
Ken came home covered in dirt.
My friends gave me this, Mom!
[GUCCHI'S MOM] I'll never
forget how happy he was
holding that little sparkly box.
[CHUTA] That sounds
like the time capsule
we all put together.
So Gucchi had it.
He must've gone back and dug it
up after we finished burying it.
[DOLUGH] That explains
why we couldn't find it!
[GUCCHI'S MOM] For years, the
box sat alone in Ken's old room.
But yesterday, I heard
a strange sound in there.
And when I checked,
the box was gone.
[GUCCHI'S MOM]
These things were in its place.
There's no earthly reason this
button should be in our house,
because he had it
pinned to his backpack
the morning he went
on that field trip.
It's like... he's alive.
Somehow, the fun
memories he had with you
are keeping his spirit alive.
[CHUTA] I want to tell her
how right she really is.
But for Gucchi, I can't.
[GUCCHI'S MOM]
Oh, Chuta.
If my Ken really did come back,
do you think you'd still
be friends with him?
Yes!
[RIGGS] I can't believe the
captain of the DeMille vessel
was a childhood friend
of Officer Kokonose.
And that's not even the
weirdest thing about all this.
Why's his picture
in that old file?
Let see, how to
explain that? You see--
Wait, Chief! Someone
from HQ just boarded!
Greetings!
The name's Inspector Belalugo,
with Internal Affairs.
Mothers sent me.
Chuta!
Now's your chance to learn
how to write up a report!
She's just gonna mock me.
"What? You don't know
how to write a report?
Go disappear and die."
[chuckles nervously]
I wanted to ask
about earlier today.
If you were just pretending
to be knocked out
for the kidnappers,
why didn't you fight
back any sooner?
Because I wanted them to take me
to their ship's captain first.
Oh, right.
Also, it gave me a chance to
see how you would hold up
under the enemy captain's
attempts at manipulation.
Had you taken his deal,
I would've made sure
you were dishonorably
discharged from elDLIVE.
What? You mean you're
still testing me?
[MISUZU]
That's right.
But I'm happy to say that
this time you passed.
I see you in a new light.
Why do you always
have to put me down?
Wait, uh, what's that?
That I see you in a new light.
Hold on! What?
She's never
complimented you before.
[MISUZU]
Can I finish eating my lunch?
Uh, Sonokata, your cheek.
[CHUTA chuckles]
[MISUZU]
Hey! Don't laugh at me!
[CHUTA] If Sonokata's
finally warming up to me,
maybe we'll get
along, after all.
Chuta!
[BELALUGO] Hold it right there,
Misuzu Sonokata!
You're under arrest on suspicion
of aiding and abetting
a known murderer.
Handcuffs, please.
What? Sonokata's under arrest?
[BELALUGO]
Hmm. Yes.
[CHUTA]
This salmon bento's really good.
[MISUZU]
What? It is?
[CHUTA] I heard saké
lees can help your skin.
[MISUZU]
Uh! Officer Kokonose!
That is more than enough
saké talk for today!
[DOLUGH]
Next time, on elDLIVE :
"Something to Believe
In: Part One"!
[CHUTA]
That's crazy!