[STUDENTS chattering]
[YAMANAKA]
Quiet down, kids!
Please extend a nice, warm
Shirobori Middle School welcome
to our three new
transfer students!
Uh, Tateyan?
[TATEYAN] Um, Ninotchka,
I know you just got here,
but would you be
Futsal Club manager?
What?
Huh? He wants what?
That guy's a creep.
Hey, no flirting
in class, Tateyan.
But you said to welcome her!
[STUDENTS laughing]
The guy has no shame.
I like that new transfer boy.
If he's got a body
to match that face,
then I think we're in business!
I don't like a man with
too many muscles.
[DOLUGH] Girls are really
into Doctor Love.
His good looks are
a total con job.
Underneath that handsome
is a 500-year-old pervert.
I bet I know what he's
thinking right now.
You look as radiant as ever.
Let's begin the
Taklamakan Project.
As you wish, Doctor Love.
Did you remember to bring
the tanning lotion?
Yes, of course, Doctor Love.
Great. Now take off
your clothes.
And put this on... for me.
[gasps]
[MISUZU]
Yes, Doctor Love.
[CHUTA screams]
Why am I the only
one who can see
how dangerous Doctor Love is?
[DOLUGH] Right now, everyone
thinks you're the dangerous one.
[CHUTA]
Huh?
[TOKU]
Hey, Misuzu!
If you had to rate the new
transfer boy's calf muscles
on a scale of one to ten,
would you say nines or tens?
Wow.
I didn't even know there
was a new transfer student.
It would also be good for
me if he carried around
some extra chocolate
protein shakes.
I'm so hungry; when we
clean the classroom,
will you help me rifle
through his bag
to see if he's got any left?
[MISUZU, SHIZU]
No, that would be a crime.
[VERONICA]
Well, well, well.
I didn't know Misuzu
goes to this school.
How come you never
said anything, hon?
[sighs]
Oh, wow, so you're
already friends
with one of the
transfer students?
No, she's wrong.
This is the first time I've ever
seen her. I don't know her.
That's not a bad answer.
If we were at work,
I'd use my higher rank to
commend you for quick thinking.
But just because we're now
on even ground at school...
...doesn't mean you'll beat me.
Not in math class and
certainly not in P.E, Misuzu!
[STUDENT A]
Whoa. Catfight.
[STUDENT B]
She's gonna punch her.
[CHUTA]
That's weird.
Why are those two at each
other's throats today?
What's going on?
Oh, wait, what about romance?
Will you girls also go
head-to-head over boys?
Who is that, girl?
She bothers me.
That's Toku.
Hey, no fighting!
Come on. Let's go.
I don't wanna leave.
It was just getting good!
[DOLUGH] Ninotchka's more like
a grown up than Veronica.
Yeah, you're right.
[TATEYAN]
Chuta!
Let's go!
[CHUTA]
What? Bowling!
Yeah, I cornered Ninotchka
outside the girls' room
and she said she'd come,
but only if you, Sonokata, and
the other new transfer students
also agreed to go bowl with us.
[CHUTA]
So you asked her out?
Wow.
I never knew Tateyan was
so forward with girls.
[DOLUGH]
What a smooth operator!
Don't get so down, Chuta.
It can take a long time to
get comfortable with girls.
[CHUTA] Doctor Love?
Where'd he come from?
I'm 500 years old and
still haven't performed
the reproductive act,
so my line's likely
to end with me.
But the Earth female seems drawn
to confident mates like him,
so he'll likely produce
many descendants.
Hey, Chuta, so why didn't you
tell me you knew the new guy?
Uh, I don't know. I just
met him for the first time.
Well, you seem weird
and fun, just like Chuta.
I'm Tateyan!
Hello, and my name's
Takurama-something.
I forget. Look, my real name
is Taklamakan Strangelove.
How could you forget
your own alias?
[TATEYAN]
That's a long name, bro.
I think I'll call you Takkun.
Takkun, huh.
[TATEYAN]
Takkun, you wanna bowl with us?
[LOVE]
Sure.
[TATEYAN]
So, Chuta.
I still need you to do
a huge favor for me
and ask Sonokata or else
Ninotchka won't come!
Please!
You see, I've never
talked to her,
but you guys seem tight,
like a married couple.
Uh, we're co-workers.
Ask her yourself!
[MISUZU]
I think I'll pass.
[CHUTA]
I'm a pushover.
That a hard no, or will
you at least consider it?
Veronica, Ninotchka,
and Doctor Love
have said they're all coming.
C'mon, it'll be fun.
I just don't see
any point in going.
[CHUTA]
Please, Sonokata?
I said no thank you.
[CHUTA]
Fine.
And besides, why couldn't you
ask me this in person?
The Chief frowns on
using your police badge
for personal business.
I don't have a choice!
You said that you
don't like me near
because of the smell of my SPH.
[gasps]
[MISUZU]
No.
Like I said before,
that was a simple
misunderstanding.
I don't believe you.
Especially after you
made a big show
about putting up with it
just for our mission.
That was, like...
I was just...
Why are you still wearing
that stupid nose plug?
Well, I wear it because
I-I looked in the mirror...
...and thought I was
missing something.
Are you saying that nose
plug's a fashion accessory?
Uh... yeah.
Well! Then it looks bad!
What do you know
about looking good?
You're just a stinky
middle school boy!
How many times have I said
don't use these badges
for personal business?
[CHUTA]
Chief Laine?
That is an elDLIVE badge,
not a cellphone.
C'mon, show some respect.
Now, since I heard everything,
and I'm your superior officer,
Misuzu, I order
you to go bowling
You gotta learn to communicate
with the other team.
They might save
your life someday.
Plus, bowling is fun.
Chief, I don't wanna go.
Oh, one more thing.
We've detected very
weak traces of SPH
at the bowling alley
you'll be visiting.
The data's so faint it
could just be signal noise,
but check it out while
you're there, just in case.
[MISUZU]
Fine. If it's work, I'll go.
All right. Happy rolling!
I'm glad it all worked out.
Guess so. This will be fun.
Don't worry, Chief. I'm sure
that little signal is nothing.
You can never be too sure.
[VERONICA] All right,
this is gonna be awesome!
I'm glad we could
all make it here.
Hey, beats doing homework!
It's been a hundred years
since I last went bowling.
Wait, are you serious?
Sonokata, you've gone
bowling before, right?
Yes. But I'm just here to
investigate that signal.
[CHUTA grunts]
[RADIO GUEST]
So I get to the airport,
and the place is just
swarming with cops!
I almost have a heart attack!
Turns out, mob bosses
from all over the world
were coming to Japan!
[DJ] Whoa, whoa whoa hold
on. Those rumors are true?
[RADIO GUEST]
Guess so!
Just wish I knew why
Italians mobsters
were meeting here
when I need to fly!
All right, no SPH
detected here.
Yeah, I didn't see
anything either.
[LOVE] Same. The place
is criminal-free.
[NINOTCHKA] It feels so nice to
all work together to solve this.
[CHIPS] Just like Chief said,
it's only signal noise, chu!
Hey! What were guys doing?
Let's roll some balls!
[DOLUGH]
He's right, Chuta.
The investigation is done.
Now we can have fun!
Okay, but don't get too excited.
Chief doesn't like
us messing around.
[TONTO]
Yay, Chief! Another strike!
[yelps]
[TONTO]
You rock at casual Earth sports!
[CHUTA]
He's here?
[laughs]
[CHUTA]
Wha--?
[laughs]
[CHUTA]
Huh?!
What the heck are Chief and the
ship's crew doing down here?
Doctor Love, are you certain
there's no one bad
in this alley?
I'm fairly certain
there's not one bowler
or snack bar patron
worth investigating.
Yeah, we know they're okay,
but Tonto and Riggs sure stand
out from everyone else here.
[DOLUGH]
They are clearly aliens.
What cosplay is that?
Wow, they look so real.
It's not a problem, Chuta.
See, people might think
they're a little weird,
but they'll never think
they're actual aliens.
[LAINE]
Hey, what took ya so long?
I didn't know you were
gonna be here, too.
We didn't know we
were going, either,
until this whole
thing came up today.
But as the bureau's resident
bowling enthusiasts,
we couldn't stay up in orbit
while you kids get
to have all the fun.
Yeah, but what about
the investigation?
Oh, so you know
these guys, too?
Uh, yeah, they're
friends-of-friends-of-friends.
They're also the president
and line workers
at the bento box factory
where my mom works part-time.
That's right. Ignore me
and go with what she said.
I just met these
normal people, too.
[TATEYAN]
Uh.
Boy, that is amazing cosplay!
Thanks, we get
that all the time.
Don't worry about us, guys,
you won't even know
that we're here.
Now go have fun!
[CHUTA]
Huh?
You're bowling in
the next lane,
how in the world
could we miss you?
[TATEYAN]
Yeah!
[CHUTA groans]
Strike!
Oh, so close!
Pick up the spare, Nino!
[LITTLE GIRL A]
Look what I got!
[LITTLE BOY A]
Cool balloon!
No matter how hard
I hit, it won't pop!
How cruel.
Well, he can't fight back
or else he'll blow his cover.
That balloon is mine.
Please give it back.
Sure!
Chips, are you okay?
All I want is to bowl,
like a normal humanoid, chu.
C'mon, Riggs, that's an
easy spare to pick-up!
Okay. So far,
Tateyan's in the lead.
[DOLUGH] The elDLIVE people
aren't scoring as high
as I thought they
would, Chuta.
Yeah, you're right.
Since I'm on top,
I'll celebrate by hitting the
head for a minute or ten!
Have fun expelling
your bodily waste.
[TATEYAN laughing]
That's a very
straight-forward young man.
He's a good guy.
He's exactly what I feared
middle school boys are like
and it's gross.
Why did you ever agree
to go bowling with him?
You had said we needed to
get used to life on
Earth, Veronica,
and this seemed like
a good opportunity
for us to get acclimated.
True.
The competition is all right,
but I hate that we're
bowling with a handicap.
Handicap?
To keep it interesting,
we have a rule that
the only way you can score
is to make a split
on your first throw.
[CHUTA] You intentionally leave
a gap between the pins?
Why would you want to do that?
Yup! And you're not
allowed to use SPH to do it.
The game's actually more
challenging this way.
[CHUTA]
Why are they all so weird?
I'm playing with normal rules.
Except I throw the ball
with just one finger.
Well, of course you are!
Why not?
When I roll, I close my good eye
and use just the pinky
on my left hand!
Where'd you guys learn to play?
With the handicap in effect,
my old nemesis Misuzu
and I are neck and neck.
But that...
...ends right now.
I'll beat you so big
it won't be close.
[DOLUGH] Veronica's really
egging her on, huh.
Um, why are you two always
at each other's throats?
I'm no mad. I just want to point
out that she's hopeless.
[CHUTA]
Oh.
You see, I'm a descendant
of the Kushutonians,
who once used their
military skill
to bring peace to the Polar
Galaxy for over 30 centuries.
Kushutonian DNA's also referred
to as "Victory Genes."
Frankly, winning
is in our blood.
So I am not going
to lose to Misuzu!
You think bowling
skill is genetic?
It's a vast universe, with
many dumb ways of thinking.
[VERONICA] Best of all, both of
my parents are Kushutonian,
so at the molecular
level, I'm, like,
pretty much one big
victory gene!
I am a true blue... pureblood!
Score that, bitches.
That's a rather
flimsy justification
for this level of passion
against Officer Sonokata.
This is just a hunch,
but I assume something
major happened in their past
to cause this discord.
[coughing]
You okay?
[NINOTCHKA]
Fine.
Am I in the right ballpark?
Oh, c'mon, tell us what
happened with them, please?
Uh. Um, well, so... one time--
[BOTH]
Nino.
[NINOTCHKA gasps]
I didn't tell 'em anything!
[CHUTA squeals]
Keep asking stupid questions,
and Misuzu won't be the
only one I beat today.
Um, Chief Laine, help!
Wow, these dumplings are great!
If you can appreciate that
taste, you've got potential!
[laughs]
Keep that oil coming', Tonto!
Sure!
They're not even looking
in this direction!
Hey, who is that?
[CHIPS] Now I can finally
enjoy bowling night
with my friends, chu!
Wait, no. Not this.
Oh, look, it's Sonokata's Mom.
[MOM ROBOT]
Misuzu, it's your mama, chu.
I'm here to bowl. Skaa.
My mama?
You and your daughter
have the same eyes!
Yeah, they look so alike.
I can't tell which one's Misuzu.
Veronica, that's not very nice.
[chuckles nervously]
Now then, I will go full-power
and surpass all your
bowling scores, chu!
Let's bowl!
[CHIPS]
Bowl--! Chu?
[screaming]
[CHIPS]
Ow-ow-ow-ow-ow-chu.
I never knew re-stacking
bowling pins
was such an involved process.
Chu?
I found a bad guy.
Exporting Earth
insects off-planet
is against the law, chu!
Hands up, pal!
I'm with Space Police
elDLIVE, chu!
Looks like I just caught
you red-handed, chu!
If you resist, you could
face additional charges
and mandatory fines.
So please don't do that, chu.
Um, anything you
say can and will
be used against you
in the court of law.
Well, technically,
inter-galactic court.
Help me! Chu!
[TATEYAN] What's wrong
with Sonokata's mom?
She's just tired, is all.
She had to work a double
shift at the factory.
[CHUTA] And the chill between
Misuzu and Veronica
has just gotten colder.
[DOLUGH]
I'm worried Misuzu might snap.
Hey, Misuzu.
How about the loser
has to publicly grovel
at the winner's feet.
If you want to act like a child,
let's raise the stakes.
Loser grovels and has
to go around the Bureau
blowing a chikuwa
with their nose.
'Kay, I'm scared now!
Whoever wins this will end up
losing part of her
soul in the process!
[VERONICA]
Watch this!
I'm going to intentionally
roll a seven-ten split!
Behold the victory
genes of a 100%
pure-blooded Kushutonian!
Wait, you're not a
pureblood, anymore.
What?!
No! I didn't wanna strike!
Oh, wow.
What are you talking about, Doc?
Remember a few days back?
The remote control SPH
incident left you near death.
I was forced to replace
your failing organs
with artificial ones.
They should finish adapting
to your body very soon.
That's not fair.
No! I'm not a pure girl anymore!
What does she mean by pure?
What a quack!
[VERONICA]
I'm gutted.
Well, at least you're
alive, Veronica!
Chuta's right.
We're all so relieved to see you
back on your feet right away.
You really were?
[NINOTCHKA]
Of course!
Feel better now?
[MISUZU]
Move.
It's my turn. And you're
blocking the lane.
Misuzu!
And how can you call
yourself a doctor
when you keep secrets from
your patients like that?
Sorry, I know it was unusual,
but the prospect of treating
you with that technique
was such an exciting callenge.
Basically, I got tunnel
vision and forgot to tell you.
But I learned a lot!
Doctor Love isn't a
very traditional doctor.
I promise to be more upfront.
In fact, I'll start right now.
May I have a moment, Sonokata?
What is it?
That nose plug you've
been wearing lately.
Did you know...
...that it's actually
a nose accessory
Tikvahkians wear when
they come of age?
There's a risk that if you
keep it on for too long,
your nose will close up
and you'll lose your
sense of smell.
[grunts]
[MISUZU]
I know all that.
I wear it off-and-on
as a fashion accessory.
Leave me alone.
C'mon, I'll buy you a soda.
[DOLUGH]
Look at Misuzu's nose!
[NOSE PLUG ALIEN]
Congratulations!
Tikvahkian tribesman!
You have finally reached
manhood. Hooray for you...
The coming of age
ceremony begins
with the Tikvahkian man's
first release of SPH.
Then, three days later, the nose
plug robot self-destructs.
That's everything I know.
[NOSE PLUG ALIEN]
Bye-bye!
[CHUTA]
Uh, Sonokata. Do I still smell?
[groans]
So you really are
repulsed by me...
[MISUZU]
No!
I wasn't reacting to your
smell, it was just an itch.
I'm going to bowl now,
so don't stand so close.
Misuzu?
[BOTH scream]
[DOLUGH]
Sympathy!
[TATEYAN]
Huh?
My hair!
Sonokata!
[VERONICA]
Misuzu!
[chuckles]
Hey, I thought you
were gonna help her!
I am.
I'm making her dumb, arrogant
face more pleasant to look at.
Don't worry about her.
The very reason I came today
is in case Sonokata experienced
any health problems
in her return to work.
Doctor Love. Always one
step ahead, aren't ya?
[ringing]
What? Picking up an
unidentified SPH signal!
[LAINE] It's coming
from inside the wall.
[WOMAN B]
Let's change bowling nights.
[MAN C]
Yep.
[ALL gasp]
[LEBOWNIANS]
Chips. Chips. Chips...
I just can't get enough
of this matcha, chu.
All right! Let's get
this party started!
[LAINE]
Well, that was interesting.
The bowling alley was
actually just a front
the Lebownians were using to
smuggle out Earth insects.
They hid their operation behind
special SPH-blocking walls.
We never would've found them
had Sonokata not
busted a hole in one.
So well done, gang.
[ALL]
Yoyosa!
And right after coming
back to work. Nice job.
Yeah, yeah.
Thanks, but breaking that
wall was just an accident.
That you were unconscious
was also strange.
How are you?
You were having such a hard
time breathing back there.
[CHUTA] Oh, no!
My smell's getting worse!
[MISUZU]
I'm anemic.
That's all guys.
If I take some iron
supplements, I'll be fine.
[CHUTA]
You're still lying!
Do you really not want them
to know that you can't work
because of my SPH smell?
Huh...
[LOVE] Well, that settles that.
I'm giving you a physical.
[CHUTA, MISUZU]
Uh?
As a doctor, your health
is my highest priority.
Ha! Have fun, Misuzu.
No, really, I'm fine.
Plus, my primary
physician is Doc Isaac.
Let me be more clear.
As a doctor, it is essential
that I thoroughly examine
your naked body.
[CHUTA]
My nightmare's come to life!
Stay back!
Whoa, be careful there!
No way, Chief!
I love that SPH glow.
I want to find the SPH veins
under your armpits
and stroke them.
[MISUZU]
I'll blast you, I swear!
Her armpits?
He sure has a way of
making non-erotic things
sound very creepy.
That's right. Teach 'em
not to mess with us girls!
All I wanna do is reach up
your sleeve and stroke you.
Back! I mean it!
No holes in the spaceship!
No blasting, chu!
[chuckling]
Doctor Love's more
agile than I expected.
Don't admire him,
do somethi-- Ah!
[CHUTA] Oh, man. I can't
believe I made Sonokata faint.
As if I wasn't already
self-conscious enough
about my body odor!
[CHUTA] Remember Sonokata
blasting off Tateyan's hair?
Well, the good news
is Doctor Love
used his latest hair
growth technology
to get it back to the orange
mop we all know and love.
But now, sometimes, he acts
like a different person.
[TATEYAN]
Next time on elDLIVE ...
[MISUZU] I could swear there
were still three left.
Oh, well, thanks, Nino.
[NINOTCHKA]
No problem!
Apparently, Inspector Chips
likes yours so much,
it's all he's drinking now.
[MISUZU]
What?
[DOLUGH] Next time on elDLIVE :
"Capture That Face!"
[CHIPS]
Ooh! Delicious, chu!