You guys, this is bad, chu!
Looks like Doctor
Love's got more
than just one bad guy
after him, chu!
Who the hell do
you think you are?
I could ask the same of you.
Who are you people?
We're with Space Police elDLIVE.
And you're under arrest
on suspicion of murder.
[MAN]
Huh, Space Police, you say.
I take it the guy in the
suit's not with you?
Dammit!
You ruined everything
I've been working on, kid!
Explain this to me, then:
How great of a plan is it when
it hinges on a frail old man?
Oh, shut up!
I didn't need him,
I just needed his brain!
It was the key to the
gate, and with it,
I coulda got my hands
on the treasure!
Treasure?
I'm completely lost.
Whatever it is, losing it's
made him really angry.
And I know I'd be angry, too,
if I lost what I wanted.
Oh, my.
Seems both the Space Police
and the criminal underworld
were after you.
So you hid yourself
in this tiny room.
Then you finally found a way
out, but it was all pointless.
I'm sorry you had such
a sad end, Doctor Love.
All right, kid,
I've heard enough.
Now die!
What the hell?
Oh, man!
I can be quite creative.
Shut up!
Oh, crap!
[MAN] You have a unique
iris. Amber in color.
And with that distinguishing
line in the lower half.
I never expected to see it here.
It's a shame I don't have the
time to study it properly.
Oh, well, maybe next time.
What the hell is this?
[IRWIN screams]
[ALL gasp]
[VERONICA]
All right, that's enough!
I wanna see both
hands in the air!
Resist and we'll use force!
Officer Kokonose,
you stay up here.
Yoyosa!
Ninotchka, Chips, let's go!
[VERONICA]
You're under arrest for murder.
For murder? How so?
[VERONICA]
Quiet!
Well, that was easy, Chuta.
Maybe, but we needed to
bring in Doctor Love alive
to clear Sonokata
with Internal Affairs.
Now I don't know how we're
supposed to save her.
[screams]
Why am I here?
Someone get me down!
[NINOTCHKA, VERONICA,
CHIPS gasp]
[CHUTA gasps]
The hell's going on? Where am I?
He's still alive?
[IRWIN]
Hey! Who are you kids?
And why are you just standing
there when I'm up here?!
Cut me down!
[yelps]
Dead body!
See, girls, I didn't kill him.
Nino! Arrest that
guy to be safe!
Uh, yoyosa!
What's going on?
What did you do to him
in that explosion?
[MAN]
I'll explain.
The blast contained a
unique SPH removal beam
to cleanse his body.
Someone else has been
controlling him from afar.
Wait, some kind of
remote control SPH?
[MAN]
Exactly.
As you imply, it's an SPH
that allows the
individual emitting it
to control the actions
and personality
of whomever absorbs it.
You can tell if
someone's absorbed it
by the amber-colored membrane
that will form in their eyes.
Until now, though,
I'd only heard of it existing
in a laboratory setting.
Besides the remote control SPH,
this criminal is an otherwise
normal, boring Earthling.
So then, he's no mastermind!
[MAN]
Exactly.
This makes me worry
about Doctor Love.
Someone unusual's
out to get him.
The nerve of you!
Aren't you the one who left his
body a bloody mess down here?
[MAN]
That's right.
But that's not his real body.
It's just waste
material left over
from the reconstruction
procedure.
What?
[MAN] During reconstruction,
there was an unexpected anomaly.
Basically, all the new cells
separated from the old ones.
Like shedding a skin.
Wait, what are you getting at?
[MAN]
What I'm saying is,
the doctor you seek is
standing right here.
[ALL]
Huh?
[CHIPS]
Huh?!
You put too much trust
in what you can see.
[VERONICA]
Chips, compare his SPH
to what's on file
for Doctor Love!
Yoyosa!
[screams]
It's a perfect match!
He's telling the truth!
He is Doctor Love, chu!
No way! He looks nothing
like his doubles!
So you're really him?
Taklamakan Strangelove,
but in a younger body?
[LOVE]
Mhm.
But why change your
appearance so dramatically?
Well, why not?
I mean, who wouldn't want to
be younger and healthier?
Huh?
Your SPH smells familiar.
Like Doltalian?
No, hold on.
Yeah, that's it! You're
descended from Kurzians!
Um, that's right.
See, I knew it!
That must mean your kicks
are really powerful.
Aw, you're so sweet.
That's amazing.
I can feel the coiled strength
in your upper thigh.
Ha-ha! As firm as the
whiskers of a spica seal!
The most distinctive feature
on Kurzian anatomy
is not their forehead horn,
but the abdominal
and oblique muscles
running right down the
center and meeting.
Here!
What a marvelous feeling!
Take off your clothes.
Lets see the raw state!
--[slap]
--[VERONICA] No!
Oh, right. Sorry.
I forgot.
Most humanoid
lifeforms don't like
exposing themselves
to strangers.
Sometimes my curiosity
gets excessive.
I'll kick you next time!
Does this make Doctor Love a...
He's funny, huh, Chuta?
...creep?
No, he's way worse than
a creep, he's a pervert!
Uh! Sonokata's been with him!
Misuzu, are you, ready?
Yes, Doctor Love.
[LOVE] Excellent. Then we'll
begin the Taklamakan Project.
[MISUZU]
Yes, Doctor Love.
First, take off your
clothes for me.
Of course, Doctor Love.
Now, step two of the
Taklamakan Project.
AKA: "Tarzan and Jane."
[screams]
[CHUTA] What kind of
doctor takes advantage
of his patients like that?
That's not what the project is.
Besides, when Misuzu
met with him,
the Doctor was still
an old man, Chuta.
[screams]
Get out of my mind before you
destroy it, Doctor Love!
Why the freak out, rookie?
I'm fine. It's just a
bad day-dream is all.
Well, we secured Doctor
Love in one piece.
It's time to head back.
We didn't leave this
place in one piece, though.
Since I'm not under arrest,
can you take these
off me please?
Oh, right! I guess I don't
mind taking those off!
What the--?
No! Veronica! Chips!
[NINOTCHKA]
I like seeing your body
all young and healthy,
Doctor Love.
But all I really
need is your brain.
And I can open the
pathway to the treasure.
What? Officer Ninotchcka?
[LOVE]
Observe her eyes.
She's been taken over by the
remote control SPH, as well.
[NINOTCHKA] It's hard to
run from me, Doctor.
No. She killed her!
[LOVE]
One thing I don't understand.
Remote Control SPH requires
a melding of both
parties' consciousness.
How did you cleanly take
over an officer of elDLIVE?
I'd be happy to show you
my method, Doctor Love.
We'll have lots of time because
you're coming with me.
I must decline.
Scientists always
seem to get killed
once they're deemed useless.
I don't believe I was
asking you, Doctor.
Now come with me.
This doesn't bode well for me.
[CHUTA]
Wait!
The Doctor stays right here!
Well, I forgot
all about you, boy.
Looks like you have a death
wish, Chuta Kokonose.
What happened, Ninotchka?
You were so sweet.
Doctor Love.
We need your removal beam!
We have to get the
remote control SPH
out of Ninotchka's body!
If somehow you could
wound or disable her,
that would buy me enough
time to repair the removal beam
and ready it to fire.
All right! Then it's all
riding on us. Let's go!
Right.
We're gonna stop her.
What I'm about to say
might sound a bit odd,
but I'm actually really
excited for this.
Monitaliens are one of
my research subjects.
[BOTH]
Huh?
[LOVE]
It's my good fortune
that's there's one
growing on you, Chuta.
Uh. Okay.
[NINOTCHKA]
I know you psyched yourself up,
but the smart move
would be to surrender.
You've no clue...
how strong I am!
[giggles]
Dolugh! Sew her up!
[DOLUGH]
Sympathy!
[chuckles]
[grunting]
[BOTH scream]
That Monitalien,
he hasn't been updated yet.
They'll need a miracle.
Are you okay? Chuta!
[NINOTCHKA]
Aw, what's wrong?
So much for you and your
parasite stopping me.
[CHUTA] We can't win. She's
in a whole different league.
Chuta! I'm starting
to fade away!
You have to keep
your confidence up!
[CHUTA]
I know, Dolugh, I know!
But it seems hopeless.
How can I fight against
someone who's so strong?
Chuta.
[VERONICA]
Run.
Just run... away.
Inspector Veronica?
You can't win, so run.
It's all my fault, Chuta. Sorry.
Don't say that!
[VERONICA]
Go now!
Run, Chuta.
Get outta this alive!
Save myself?
[CHUTA] But if I run away,
I'm leaving Veronica,
Doctor Love, Chips, and
Ninotchka here to die.
And what about Sonokata?
No. I'm the only one
who can help them.
It's all on me.
Chuta, you're not
going anywhere!
Just hold on!
Stay with me, Veronica.
Listen, it's all going to
be all right. I promise!
Looks like I'm coming
back into view!
The return of your confidence
has me feeling like a
million bucks, Chuta!
What happened?
I don't know. I just--
I realized I have to
believe in myself!
And that... I have
to save everyone!
You love your friends, huh?
And that's why you believe.
I don't think your confidence
has ever been stronger!
Yes. Let's go, Dolugh!
Yoyosa!
My goodness, look
who's back for more.
[DOLUGH] You can't win by
running away, Chuta.
You've gotta get behind her.
Yeah, but how?
She's looking right at us!
[DOLUGH]
Good point.
Look at those cables, Chuta!
I've got an idea!
[NINOTCHKA]
You wanna play hide-and-go-seek?
Okay then. But you're just
delaying the enevitable.
[NINOTCHKA]
A decoy made from cables?
Now, Dolugh! Blast her!
Aw, that's cute. Now watch this.
[chuckles]
Dolugh!
Too strong! Dolugh, turn away!
Can you hear me?
Dolugh!
[gasps]
[chuckles]
The air's full of burning SPH.
It smells like death.
[LOVE]
Huh?
[CHUTA]
My face... it's so hot.
What's going on?
[CHUTA]
I can't-I can't talk.
What happened to me? Dolugh.
[CHUTA]
Dolugh.
[gasps]
[CHUTA]
Dolugh?
Damage to a host and
Monitalien applies equally.
Given Dolugh's injuries,
Chuta must be in bad shape.
[CHUTA]
I-I can't breath.
[NINOTCHKA]
Monitaliens are nothing more
than useless old relics.
For a Monitalien and
its host to die in agony
is a fitting end
for both of you.
[CHUTA] So that's...
what's happening... I'm dying.
Without saving Veronica, Chips,
Ninotchka, or Sonokata.
Dammit!
[DOLUGH]
Chuta.
[CHUTA]
Uh? Dolugh, is that you?
[DOLUGH]
Lately, I've been thinking
about why you ignored the
evidence against Misuzu
and still trusted her anyway.
Are you serious?
We're both near death and
you're still bringing that up?
[DOLUGH] Not long ago,
you wouldn't have been able
to trust someone the
way you trust her.
Since joining elDLIVE,
you've changed so much.
And since you put
up walls for so long,
I'm interested any time
your personality changes.
I think I know what's behind
this. Would you like to hear it?
Since you like Misuzu,
you believe in her.
And that makes you trust
that she wouldn't do wrong
without good reason.
And because Doctor Isaac
believes in you,
he thought you'd be able
to help clear her name.
That's why he told
you Miszu's secret
about needing the medicine.
And now, you wanna
save more than just her.
I don't think about it.
I'm just simply... doing what
my heart tells me to.
And that's... to save everyone!
[DOLUGH] Yes, that's it.
You want to save everyone.
But in order to
get to this point,
you had to believe in Misuzu,
and in turn, yourself.
Do you understand, Chuta?
It doesn't matter who it is.
Believing in someone is
an expression of hope.
I do believe.
[DOLUGH]
And now, I believe in you, too.
[CHUTA]
Dolugh.
[DOLUGH] My hope is to remain
in a symbiotic relationship
with you and no one else!
[DOLUGH] Killing current
host's life support process.
Activating survival program.
It's evolving.
What's this?
When the host of a
Monitalien is dying,
the creature will
attempt to escape
its own pending destruction
by using any remaining
energy to quickly evolve.
It's a fail-safe device.
[NINOTCHKA] After all that,
you're still clinging to life?
I'll break your spirit, too!
You half-dead freaks!
[gasps] Deflected?
You underestimate it
at your own peril.
It isn't just trying to survive.
It's looking for a new
host that it can attach to.
[DOLUGH]
Next host detected.
Calculating necessary evolution
and transformation steps.
[gasps]
[DOLUGH]
Attack.
What the--? What was that?
[LOVE]
What a remarkable recovery.
[DOLUGH]
Transformation complete.
Attack!
[LOVE] This Monitalien
evolutionary form
is the most advanced of
all lost Griffith technology.
All that's left now is to
toy with its host target
until she gives up.
[DOLUGH]
Attack.
Forget it, pal! No way
I'm giving up this body!
[DOLUGH]
Attack.
[CHUTA] I thought you
wanted to stay with me.
[DOLUGH]
New Host disabled. Attack.
[CHUTA]
Stop it, Dolugh. Please, stop!
[DOLUGH]
Attack.
Adjusting aim.
Sto--
--[CHUTA] Dolugh. Stop it!
--[DOLUGH] Host secured.
[CHUTA] Come on!
Snap out of this, Dolugh!
[DOLUGH]
Attack.
Dolugh!
This isn't who you really are!
I... believe in you!
[DOLUGH]
Sympathy!
[groans]
[CHUTA coughing]
Are you back now?
I'm back!
And you're really you?
I really am me again, Chuta.
Dolugh, I'm glad
you're back to normal.
You really had me worried
there for a bit, buddy.
Well done.
You have just managed a
Reconnection with a Monitalien.
What the heck does that mean?
[DOLUGH] I evolved and
left for a new host.
Then I changed my mind
and came back!
And that's how rare?
[LOVE]
It's extraordinarily rare.
Once a Monitalien prepares
to leave its host,
the chance of him
bringing it back
with a strong sympathetic
response is a mere 0.02%.
A strong sympathetic
response did that?
What would've happened
if it wasn't strong?
You would be dead!
What? Now you tell me?
Even though our chances
for success were low,
we had no choice but to try it
if we wanted to
save our friends.
Wait, uh, I think I get it now.
What you said before.
[DOLUGH] Believing in someone
is an expression of hope.
And now, I believe in you, too.
My hope is to remain in
a symbiotic relationship
with you and no one else!
You were talking
about Reconnection.
You know I never gave
up believing in you, Chuta,
and that's why I knew
we would reconnect.
And you kept believing in me!
And it all happened because our
shared sympathy was so powerful!
[NINOTCHKA chuckling]
I'm glad you guys're back
to being weak and pathetic.
Makes things easy for me.
[CHUTA]
No.
We're much different
now. Stronger.
I can feel it.
Isn't that right, Dolugh?
Yes! That's right!
[giggles]
[CHUTA] Here's that
rice-cakes-in-soup dish
you've been talking
about, Chief.
It's actually called zoni .
[LAINE] But the one
I liked had darker broth.
And it was sweeter, too!
[DOLUGH]
Next time on elDLIVE :
"Something to Believe
In: Part Three"!
[MISUZU]
That's red bean soup.