[CHUTA]
Freeze!
[DOLUGH]
Are you sure you shouldn't call
Misuzu or Chips for back-up?
I'm perfectly capable of
handling this, Dolugh.
Besides we're not in Division
Two anymore, remember?
[CHUTA] You're transferring
me to Division Four?
Division Four's been
under-manned for a while now.
Don't worry, though,
it's only temporary.
What are your new
partners' names, Chuta?
I've actually never
met any of them.
Inspector Vega's the
only one to meet,
and he's heading to a
crime scene right now.
Why don't you rendezvous
with him down there?
Yoyosa!
Faster!
Yeah!
I'm with elDLIVE.
You have the right
to remain silent!
[CHUTA yelps]
No, I forgot my badge!
[CHUTA yelling]
Chuta, look!
Hey!
SPH.
He's the quickest one
we've had in a while!
Time for the big gun!
Yeah!
[DOLUGH]
Sympathy!
[CHUTA]
Freezing Gum!
You can't outrun me now.
[CHUTA gasps]
[DOLUGH]
Body substitution?
[yells]
[ALIEN CRIMINAL A]
You're finished, Space Cop!
[VEGA]
Sorry I'm late.
[CRIMINAL A]
He has back-up?
[VEGA]
You okay, Officer Kokonose?
Hello there. I'm with the
local elDLIVE Bureau.
Division Four.
Inspector Vega Victor.
[CHUTA]
Inspector Vega Victor?
He's the guy who
runs Division Four.
[CRIMINAL A growl]
SPH. Luce Bomber!
[CHUTA, DOLUGH scream]
SPH. Rossa Assalto!
You really should give up.
Resisting will make
your sentence worse.
[yells]
I messed up.
Go on, get it over with.
Chuta! It's the mark!
[CHUTA]
DeMille!
Just kill me! Rather you
do it than my bosses!
[VEGA] Believe me, pal,
having seen your rap sheet,
I'd love nothing more
than to put you down.
And at my rank, I can
do that any way I want.
However--
Oh, no! He's gonna blow up!
Watch out!
You are going... to live.
You'll atone for every
bad thing you've done.
Oh, wow.
[VEGA] So if you haven't
noticed, we're understaffed.
But even if you're just a temp,
you'll help me
with this backlog.
Um, Section Chief,
I want you to know I
appreciate your help today.
[VEGA]
Huh? What help?
I was in a tight spot,
and you saved me.
No big deal. It is all
part of the job.
Right, but now that
I think about it,
I could've died back--
It's a senior agent's job
to protect his juniors.
It's the first trial for the
new Division Four team.
Am I right?
Yes!
We're pretty close in age,
so I'm just gonna
call you Chuta.
And I'd appreciate if you
just called me Vega.
Keep it friendly.
Sir!
You're so stiff!
Just say "okay."
'Kay!
[DOLUGH]
I can feel a warm feeling
growing deep inside you, Chuta!
It's like the feeling you have
toward your Aunt Mimi,
but... different.
Dolugh, I think this
is what it feels like
to have a big brother.
[TATEYAN]
Chuta!
Wanna go to the art museum
with me this weekend?
Museum?
I saw an ad for
their new exhibit!
It'll really get the blood
pumping, if ya know what I mean!
Takkun is already in!
[CHUTA]
Uh, okay. Sure, guess I'll go.
[VERONICA]
Who knew Tateyan liked art?
Don't judge a book
by its cover.
Misuzu.
Lately, I can't help but notice
that you're always sneaking
around Chuta now.
What are you up to?
If you're implying I
like him, you'd be wrong.
[TOKU]
Oh my gosh, who is that?
That hot guy!
Toku, get back before you fall!
[CHUTA]
Vega?
Hey, Chuta.
You know him, Chuta?
Y-Yeah! Well, sort of.
Nice to meet you.
I'm Chuta's cousin, Vega.
Vega? Badass name, dude!
[SHIZU]
Is he a high-schooler?
[TOKU]
Those glasses are delish!
Well, that's great.
Chuta and Vega are
already getting along well.
Poor you. Must be lonely
without Chuta around.
Excuse me, but my
shift is starting now.
Which means that this was
all my fault the whole time.
What caused your anxiety was
a frustration with yourself.
As you sat there watching
Chuta mature by your side,
your urge to mature
yourself just intensified.
It's a completely
natural response.
[sighs]
[LAINE]
Misuzu!
You see Chuta around?
[MISUZU]
No.
Oh, well, when you
do see him next,
can you give him this for me?
I wanted to give it to
him myself earlier.
but I hadn't received approval
from the higher-ups yet.
I'm sorry for all
the trouble I caused
when I said your
SPH smelled awful.
I'm sorry for all
the trouble I caused
when I said your
SPH smelled awful.
'Kay!
Officer Kokonose!
Oh, hi, Sonokata!
I'm sorry, but he's not here.
Okay. It's not important.
Oh, hey. Thanks for
loaning him to me.
Of course.
In fact, I don't mind if you
keep him here permanently.
That's great.
He'd be a huge help.
So is he down on Earth?
Oh, crap, that's right!
I got invited, too!
Great! I'm late. Sorry,
I gotta go. See ya!
[VEGA]
Hey, I'm here!
Veeyan, you're late, dude.
[VEGA]
Sorry, guys.
Veeyan?
Well, his name's Vega!
Oh, have you met
Takkun here yet?
Uh, no.
Hello, Senpai.
Hello.
Doctor Love's older,
but he calls Vega "senpai."
Five hundred years old.
Guys, let's go! He-he!
Wait till ya see
these paintings!
[clears throat]
[CHUTA, TATEYAN]
Whoa-ho! Oh, yeah!
This is a new low,
even for those perverts.
How can this turn them on?
[TATEYAN]
Whoa! This looks like Ninotchka!
Right, Chuta?
[CHUTA]
Holy crap, you're right.
It's like-like she posed for it!
[DOLUGH] Your heart's
beating really fast!
[NINOTCHKA squeals]
[TATEYAN]
This looks like Misuzu!
[LOVE]
Indeed. It's very accurate.
He would only know that if...
Doctor Love has seen her naked!
[DOLUGH] Well, of course he's
seen her with her clothes off.
He is a doctor.
[TATEYAN]
And this looks like Veronica!
Ah! Everything looks so real!
I wanna touch it!
Yes, it's perfect.
How do you know?
That painting is all wrong!
You're here?!
[LOVE]
Oh, look, it's all the girls.
No way! My body looks
way better than that!
You're even hotter than that?!
Um, we didn't know you
girls were coming, too.
I swear I didn't invite them!
I didn't give anything away!
These boys are just
stupid animals.
Perving out over some
dumb old paintings.
[TATEYAN chuckles]
I've suspected for a while
that Officer Kokonose
is a deviant.
What? That's not true!
I think she's got you
on this one, Chuta.
What about you?
What's your excuse for being
so immature, Inspector Vega?
He has none!
He's not that much older
than Chuta, anyway.
[VEGA]
No! Wait, hold on!
I came more as a chaperone.
Wow! Well, that's a big lie!
At least they're honest.
Uh, hey, I really think
you're overreacting.
[buzzing]
[CHUTA]
"elDLIVE is hiding what happened
at the Mount Taketori incident"?
You can't check your
badge monitor here.
There are civilians
all over the place.
It's against the rules.
[CREW MEMBER A]
Captain!
Urgent message from HQ!
Okay, send it on through.
[CREW MEMBER A]
Woohoo!
It looks like they want us to
set a course again for Earth!
What? Strange.
Okay, so why's the
boss so obsessed?
It's just another boring planet.
Maybe it has some
treasure we need?
[GUCCHI]
Maybe she's right.
But there's still
the bigger mystery
of why DeMille saved me
back on Mount Taketori.
[CREW MEMBER A]
There's more!
Looks like we're
going back to Earth
as part of a full-on
invasion force!
[GUCCHI] This is way
bigger than I thought.
I have to get a message to
Chuta, before it's too late.
So this e-mail, what do
you think it's all about?
Do you really think Chief and
the other bosses at elDLIVE
are hiding something big about
the Mount Taketori incident?
I don't think Chief Laine
even knows about it.
Maybe he does, but the
whole thing's top secret?
Whoa, sorry!
Hey, it's fine.
Chuta, look!
[CHUTA]
Whoa!
Wait a minute!
Isn't that the program
to the art exhibit?
Are you allowed to
look at that at work?
Oh! Yeah, of course.
'Cause, uh, it's
research material
to help me learn more
about culture on Earth!
He's definitely lying.
[chuckles nervously]
[CHUTA]
Hey, Vega.
Do you believe that everything
here is on the up-and-up?
Okay, where is this going?
Well, what if they had
info about your past,
but wouldn't tell you.
Would that be
normal around here?
[VEGA]
We're in law enforcement, Chuta.
Of course we keep secrets.
But if you're as concerned
as I think you are,
why not do a little
poking around the Bureau
to see what turns up?
[CHUTA]
Investigate on my own, huh?
What would you say is our single
biggest case? DeMille, right?
[VEGA]
Yeah.
As long as they're out
there running free,
this galaxy will never
know true peace.
I'd do anything to
bring them down.
And that would even include
giving up my own life.
[DOLUGH]
What are you going to do, Chuta?
[CHUTA] First, I'm tracking down
whoever sent me this email.
The key is to find out
where it came from.
That should be a clue
to the person's identity.
Why don't you ask
Chief Laine first?
Because even if I did, there's
no way he'd tell me anything.
No, Vega has it right.
To find the truth, I'll just
have to investigate on my own.
And you know what, Dolugh.
If it was sent to
my police badge,
then the sender must be
someone on the Jeanrenoi-R.
[MELIES yells]
What's wrong?
[MCCLANE]
Comms are malfunctioning!
SPH Compass system is
non-functional, too!
Melies, status report!
[MELIES]
Bad news, Chief!
I think we got hit with
a computer virus!
[LAINE]
Where?
The data processing room!
Riggs, isolate that system.
Everything else to
the back-up net!
Yoyosa!
[LAINE] Security!
Get to Data Processing!
[TARO]
Huh?
Officer Kokonose?
Taro, hi.
Wait, Chuta's the one
who uploaded the
virus to our system?
[RIGGS]
No way.
Officer Kokonose
claims he had no clue
the badge was infected
when he plugged it in.
That he was just trying to find
out who sent him an email.
Email? What's happening now?
Massive heat source detected!
It's right on top of us!
[gasps]
[ALL gasp]
What the--? How
did they get here?
[RIGGS] It's normally impossible
to come out of warp
this close to another ship.
The virus must've been part of
a plan to get the drop on us!
They slipped by while our
SPH radar was down
and we were switching
to the back-up net!
Chief, there's an energy
surge inside that ship!
[RIGGS]
And you know what comes next!
Evasive maneuvers!
[LAINE]
Damage report!
[RIGGS]
Portside engine is out!
[MARLY] Injuries in
Community Safety Section!
What the hell?
[SPACE COP screams]
[LAINE] Send a medic
squad to those wounded!
Well, hello there, elDLIVE.
I'm commander of
this solar system's
DeMille Excursion Force,
DeMille Junior.
DeMille?
That was an impressive
introduction.
I've a flair for the dramatic.
[LAINE]
If this is a full-on invasion,
why are we even
talking right now?
What do you really want
from us, DeMille Junior?
I'm impressed, Chief.
You cut right to the chase.
We simply demand
that you hand over
the Monitalien in
your possession.
Along with its host,
Chuta Kokonose.
If you do not
meet this demand,
the invasion will
begin in earnest.
They can't!
[LAINE] Why do you want
the Monitalien so bad?
[DEMILLE JUNIOR] Let's just
say an updated Monitalien
is of great value to us.
[LAINE]
Of course it is.
And that's why we'll
never give it up.
We've already hit your ship once
and are happy to do it again.
Give them up.
True.
Based on our current
weapon systems,
it'd be impossible to
fight them head-on.
But having said that,
I still have my research
facilities left on Earth.
With those weapons,
it is possible to attack
Earth's exoatmosphere.
After that, disabling the
DeMille ship's main gun
becomes academic.
So, Chief. What's the plan?
I can't believe you're
still thinking this over.
I'm guessing you won't find many
decisions easier than this.
[LAINE] Yeah. You're
right on that count.
There's only one answer
to this situation.
All hands to battlestations!
All right, we're taking
their ship down!
[ALL]
Yoyosa!
Fire volley!
[LAINE]
You're up, Doc!
--Hell yeah!
--We did it!
[alarm sounding]
What's wrong?
[MCCLANE] Well, Chief,
they weren't kidding
about the invasion.
DeMille ships are
appearing all over Earth!
Their fleet was already here?
Tricked us again.
You do see now that
resistance is futile.
Chief, I'll give you
just one hour.
Gather the Monitalien
and Chuta Kokonose
and give them to me.
If they're not on
my ship by then,
I'll order my fleet
to attack the Earth.
[RIGGS]
An hour. Damn.
That's not enough
time for a plan B!
Crap! We're almost
down to 59 minutes!
If only Chuta hadn't
uploaded that virus!
Maybe he's a spy planted
here by DeMille!
[TONTO]
He is not a spy!
That is enough!
[door opens]
[CHUTA]
Chief Laine!
This-This is all
my fault, right?
Huh, how so?
Because of what I did...
DeMille can take over the Earth.
[VEGA]
Don't beat yourself up.
[CHUTA]
You guys.
I'm gonna turn myself
over to DeMille!
It's the best way to end this!
Oh, Chuta.
Chief Laine! Contact them!
Let DeMille know that
I'm surrendering myself!
[CHIPS] Enough crazy talk,
chu! Listen to me!
This isn't just your problem
now, Officer Kokonose!
Then what do you
think I should do?
Chief Laine, we might be
able to buy some time
by sending Chuta down to
Earth and hiding him there.
What?
And let's face it.
It's certainly safer
than staying here.
You're right, Vega.
Inspector Chips, I want
you to accompany Chuta
to the Space Café.
And don't make another move
until you hear from me.
--Yoyosa!
--No!
Let me go to them!
[BOTH groaning]
[CHIPS]
Chu.
[CHIPS] The streets
are totally empty, chu.
I'm getting a bad vibe, chu!
Huh? Officer Kokonose?
[MIMI]
"Dear Chuta.
I'm taking shelter in the
school's gymnasium."
[DOLUGH]
At least Aunt Mimi is safe.
Once again...
...because I did something
I shouldn't have,
other people suffer.
Don't think like that!
I'm starting to disappear again!
When you lose your confidence,
you also lose me!
I'm so... I'm so stupid.
It looks like a message.
[DOLUGH]
It's from Gucchi!
[CHUTA]
Huh?
[DOLUGH] He's trying
to talk to you, Chuta.
I think I can still read it.
Do you want me to?
Of course, hurry up!
[DOLUGH]
"DeMille is on the move.
They desperately
want to find Dolugh.
Your elDLIVE Bureau
is compromised.
One of its members
is a DeMille spy.
Be careful, Chuta.
Because that spy person is--"
[CHUTA]
Dolugh. Dolugh, who is it?
Dolugh! Come back!
Dolugh.
[VEGA]
Hey.
I thought Chief gave
you and Chips orders
to hide in the Space Café?
[CHUTA]
Vega. What should I do?
Chuta...
I need your advice.
What would you do if
you were in my shoes?
[VEGA] I don't know.
That's a hard one.
Officer Kokonose!
Why're you here?
[MISUZU]
Same reason as you, Inspector.
I was worried sick
about Officer Kokonose.
Uh, just like everyone
else is at the Bureau.
Ah, that's just for show.
They won't let me
do what's right.
You know the truth,
right, Sonokata?
About the accident on Mount
Taketori when I was a child?
I thought my friend died.
But he ended up an executive
officer with DeMille.
It wouldn't be weird for elDLIVE
to be looking into
all this, would it?
But it feels like Chief and
everybody else wants me close,
but not too close.
Kokonose.
Chief gave me this
to give to you.
I'm sorry I didn't have a chance
to give it to you sooner.
This is the complete
Mount Taketori case file.
Everything elDLIVE has on it.
I found out after he joined up.
The Taketori incident
has elements
that put it under
our jurisdiction.
Mainly, that one of
his friends survived,
and is now an
officer with DeMille.
I'm sure Chuta's even more
confused about this than we are.
I wanted to tell him what we
knew when the time was right,
but it hasn't worked out.
Like you've said,
Officer Kokonose,
everything that happened on that
mountain's a confusing mystery.
But the one thing we
do know for sure
is that aliens were
somehow involved.
He believes in me.
He believes that I
can handle the truth.
But I failed us.
[MISUZU]
Kokonose!
The only thing that matters now
is that you can
protect the Earth.
As an officer of elDLIVE!
That's right.
I can't give up now!
[CHUTA] That's right.
It's the challenge of my life,
and I'll get through it
as a member of elDLIVE!
Let's go, Sonokata!
[MISUZU]
Next time on elDLIVE :
[CHUTA, MISUZU]
"Our sympathy"!
[CHUTA] We'll protect the
Earth, no matter what!