Officer Kokonose,
we were worried about you.
Where have you been, chu?
Sorry I'm late.
[ALIEN A] I heard DeMille's
after some brat.
Goes by the name
of Chuta Kokonose.
If you ask me, we should
just hand him over.
Gimme a break.
Ya really think that DeMille's
gonna keep their promise
and leave us alone
after we give 'em this kid?
[door opens]
[ALIEN A]
Hey, they're from--
[ALIEN B]
DeMille.
We have reason to believe
that the Monitalien and its
host are hiding out here.
[DEMILLE SOLDIER B] It'll be bad
news for anyone helping them.
Monitalien? What are
you talking about?
How did DeMille manage
to find us here, chu?
Seems like it happened
a little too fast.
Huff and puff all you want,
but even if we knew where they
were, we wouldn't tell ya.
What did you say?
[GUILLERMO]
Get the hell outta here.
That's what happens
when you defy us.
You bastard!
[CHUTA]
I'm right here!
No, don't!
Those guys have nothing to do
with this. Leave 'em alone!
Ah, so you're Kokonose.
How nice of you to make our
job easy by coming forward.
Yeah, well, I don't plan on
being all that cooperative.
I'm an officer of elDLIVE.
It's my sworn duty to
protect everyone here!
And how are you going to
protect them all by yourself?
The thing is, he's
not here by himself.
Sonokata!
Stay where you are!
[VEGA]
That's enough.
Miss Sonokata.
Vega?
The nature and origin
of the flying objects
that have appeared in the sky
remain a mystery to authorities.
But we have reports
of similar incidents
occurring all around the world.
Chuta.
[LAINE] Any movement
from the DeMille ship?
No signs of it coming
after us, sir.
Well, in our current condition,
we aren't going to be
able to get very far.
It looks like they've got
us all figured out.
[grunts]
[CHIPS] Inspector Vega,
what are you doing?
[yells]
Vega, what's going on?
[VEGA] While investigating
the mysterious message
he received, Chuta Kokonose
wound up infecting
the Jeanrenoi-R's
system with a virus,
thereby putting all of
planet Earth in jeopardy.
Poor guy couldn't handle
all the guilt anymore and--
Here's what you were supposed
to be thinking right now:
"If I hand myself over to
DeMille, everyone will be okay."
In fact, I'm pretty
sure that thought's
already run through your mind.
But why?
[VEGA]
And to think...
...that's exactly how you
would've acted, too.
But if you've gone off script,
we need to rewrite the scenario.
Sonokata, what are--?
Ugh, are you still
not getting it?
It's Vega. He's the one
who's working for DeMille.
[gasps]
So Vega works... for DeMille?
Oh, no.
[DOLUGH]
"elDLIVE is compromised.
One of its members
is a DeMille spy.
Be careful, Chuta.
Because that spy person is--"
[CHUTA]
Vega. This can't be true.
You can't be a spy. How
could you trick me like that?
[VEGA] You and Dolugh will
be coming to DeMille.
If you try to resist,
I'll be forced to hurt you.
At least as much as I
can without killing you.
[MISUZU groans]
Chuta.
[CHUTA]
He's gone.
[VEGA]
Hm?
I mean Dolugh. He's gone.
What are you talking about?
[CHUTA]
Dolugh has... vanished.
He's no longer within
me. He's gone.
[VEGA] Are you actually
trying to bluff me here?
We'll find out soon enough
when we examine you.
Look, if you wanna take me,
that's fine, go ahead.
Assuming I still have
any worth left.
Without Dolugh
inside me, that is.
You know, you're really
throwing a wrench
into my plans
with this business.
I'll give you 30 minutes.
You have till then to do
whatever you gotta do
to get Dolugh back
and bring him here.
If you don't, then
everybody will die.
[CHUTA]
Sonokata, are you okay?
Yes.
But more importantly right now,
is that true about Dolugh?
[GUILLERMO]
Hey, kid.
You're one tough son of
a gun, did you know that?
Come any closer,
and I swear, I'll attack.
Oh, cool your jets. We are
not your enemy, little lady.
Now, is there anything we can
do to help you guys out?
Is Vega really part of DeMille?
No way! We worked
together in investigations.
It's impossible!
No, Inspector Vega is
a member of DeMille.
There's no question.
He attacked us just now, chu!
Really? But how?
We also have reason to believe
he's the one who
sent that email.
The one that led to
Officer Kokonose
infecting the Bureau's
system with that virus.
But wait, I was
under the impression
that all DeMille
personnel had a recorder
and a bomb planted
inside of them.
I never detected
anything like that
in Inspector Vega's
body that I know of.
[RIGGS]
We checked out his family, too.
There were no connections
to any criminal organizations.
Of course not. I happen to
know his father quite well.
In fact, he was once a highly
respected elDLIVE detective.
So nothing suspicious
about him, huh?
How could he be a spy
with a perfectly spotless
record like that?
Well, of course
he's squeaky clean.
What's that mean, Doctor Love?
Do you really think
a crime syndicate
infiltrating the police
would send a shady spy
who might set off all
kinds of alarm bells?
Yeah, good point.
It is possible Vega might
even have been " kusa ."
Kusa ?
[LOVE] During the Warring
States Period in Japan,
there were shinobi known
as kusa , or grass.
After sneaking into
enemy territory,
they would blend in with the
local farmers, create families,
and then pass their mission
on down to their children.
It's possible that not only was
his father a spy, but also,
one of his grandparents
could've been as well.
That fate may've been bequeathed
onto Vega's generation.
So it's like a ticking time bomb
was planted into
elDLIVE years ago.
To think, Inspector Vega
was-- I can't believe it!
I feel the same way as you.
However, the fact is,
he's betrayed elDLIVE,
and now the planet Earth
is in serious danger.
[CHUTA]
I can't forgive Vega.
[LAINE]
Chuta.
I want to arrest Vega
and make him pay.
And even more than that,
I want to protect the Earth.
Protect everybody!
Uh, why are you
stating the obvious?
That's right, Chuta.
Everyone here feels the exact
same way. I promise you.
Yeah, she's right, chu!
We're Space Police elDLIVE,
that's pretty much
what we do, chu!
Chips tells it like
it is, right, Chief?
Well, naturally.
Now then,
the only question is how we
ought to be approaching this
given how severely outgunned
we are at the moment.
Let's see.
I actually might have
an idea about that.
[LAINE]
Oh, yes?
Listen up.
[DEMILLE SUBORDINATE A]
So I take it you weren't able
to capture the Monitalien?
Yeah, sorry about that.
But Chuta Kokonose told
me it had vanished.
I guess you're a miserable
little spy after all.
Doesn't really matter.
Either way, that planet will
soon be a sea of flames.
[chuckles]
And I for one can't
wait to see it.
The sight of those Earthlings
scurrying around, terrified.
[LAINE] All personnel,
report to battle stations!
We'll commence our attack
on the DeMille ship shortly.
All civilians and
anyone with injuries
should get to safety
immediately!
Everybody who can fight,
check your equipment
and stand by for further orders!
[RIGGS]
But are you sure this will work?
I mean, using those guys?
There are aliens holding
grudges against DeMille
who are in hiding all
over Planet Earth.
And their numbers are great.
Those DeMille bastards!
Today's the day I'm finally
gonna show 'em who's boss!
If they help us out,
then by gosh,
we might just have a chance at
actually winning this fight!
Though no matter what,
I'm probably still gonna have
to write a formal apology.
Chief Laine!
Chuta, welcome back.
Please, you've gotta
let me fight, too!
It's too dangerous now that
you don't have Dolugh anymore.
Yeah, I know that.
But with all that Vega has done,
I really want to be able to
settle this with him myself!
Honestly, you'll
just be in the way.
But if I were to receive a
direct order from the Chief,
well then,
I suppose I would
have no objections
to backing up Officer Kokonose.
We're all part of
Division Two, chu!
Sonokata. Inspector Chips.
Here, take it.
What's this?
Hah. That is a special
gun that's capable
of shooting out SPH energy.
Figure you could use
that right aout now.
Oh, wow. Thank you!
[ALL]
All personnel ready!
All right!
Let's start our final battle
with the DeMille ship.
Objective: Arrest
Inspector Vega,
as well as DeMille Junior!
[ALL]
Yoyosa!
[DEMILLE JUNIOR] How's the Earth
Suppression Squad looking?
[DEMILLE SUBORDINATE B]
They're all ready to go.
Please, just wait!
There's still a few minutes
before the deadline is up!
[DEMILLE JUNIOR]
Begin!
[DEMILLE SUBORDINATE B]
Yes, sir!
What the--?
[DEMILLE SUBORDINATE B]
elDLIVE is attacking!
How much damage can
a damaged ship do?
[DEMILLE GUNNER A]
It's just a hologram!
What the hell--?
Great, now what?
[COMMUNICATIONS A] They're
coming from another direction!
Elmeser cannons
at full power now!
Fire!
Evade!
[COMMUNICATIONS A]
We won't make it in time!
Main engine has
sustained heavy damage!
This ship, my feline body.
The laser cannons, my cat claws.
Barrier SPH output
is now full, ribbit!
Here goes! Head right for 'em!
[COMMUNICATIONS A]
Captain, they're ramming us!
Then shoot them down!
[TONTO]
Meow!
[COMMUNICATIONS A]
It's too late!
Division Five on the enemy ship!
Yeah, Division One
is onboard now, too.
Division Two is on
the ship as well, chu.
[LOVE]
I've scanned the interior.
DeMille Junior's onboard.
[COMMUNICATIONS A] elDLIVE
has infiltrated our ship!
Find them and fire!
Kill every last one!
Earth Suppression Squad!
Burn every inch of that planet!
[COMMS SOLDIER A] This is
the Earth Suppression Squad!
We're currently being overrun
by unknown enemies--
All right now, here we go!
[ALIENS]
Yeah!
Shero, shero,
shero, shero, shero!
[DEMILLE SOLDIER K]
They've taken over the ship!
[DEMILLE SOLDIER L] Ugh!
How many of them are there?
[growling]
[VERONICA]
Obrót Akcja!
[BOTH]
SPH Blast!
No!
Aw, thanks, Nino!
It's all right.
Just leave 'em to me.
You two run ahead now, chu.
Inspector Chips!
Don't fail us.
[MOM ROBOT]
Finally.
The time has come
for me to reveal
what I'm truly capable of.
SPH weapon in standby, chu!
And now to initiate the
program drive, chu!
[CHIPS]
Chu!
[BOTH gasp]
[CHUTA]
Vega!
Is Dolugh back yet, or not?
What a shame.
You've forgotten our deal.
[yells]
[MISUZU yells]
Time to end this.
[screams]
Vega!
[VEGA] My father gave his all,
even to the very end.
As an elDLIVE detective,
he was second to no one.
And honestly, that's all I ever
wanted to be my whole life.
Vega.
[VEGA] I never wanted
to be a DeMille spy.
I just wanted to work in
elDlive. And help stop crime.
Ah, but then you
had to come along.
Everything's been ruined
now... all because of you!
But why didn't you just
try to quit being a spy?
I mean, you don't have
one of their recorders
or a bomb planted
inside of you, right?
[VEGA] DeMille's been
monitoring my entire family
back on our home planet
this whole time.
[CHUTA]
Your family?
[VEGA]
Which means they're hostages.
Oh, no.
If you were in my position,
you'd do the same thing.
There's no way you'd ever
risk defying DeMille.
[CHUTA]
Yeah, that might've been true.
Before I joined elDLIVE.
But now I'm different!
No matter how dire
the circumstances,
I'm not giving up
till the bitter end!
How very childish of you.
Let's say you don't give up,
what happens after that?
[CHUTA] I'm gonna
beat... the bad guys..
...and save the people
important to me!
[VEGA] You think you can have
both? How greedy of you.
Yeah, well, you may be right.
But I do know one thing.
I am not going to regret it!
I wanna eat pasta, curry,
and hamburger steak!
I don't wanna pick just one!
Besides, I know I'm
gonna end up regretting
just picking one of those dishes
so I should keep all the
options on the table,
and just prepare all
of those dishes!
Officer Kokonose.
[CHUTA] But to regret
not doing something?
That's something... that I...
...never, ever...
want to do... again!
[DOLUGH]
Sympathy!
Dolugh!
You know, eating pasta,
curry, and hamburger steak
would definitely be
eating too much, Chuta.
Nah.
If I can't finish it all myself,
then I'll just share some
with the neighbors,
it's as simple as that.
[gasps] Officer Kokonose!
I'm happy to see that
Dolugh has finally returned.
Now I can take you
both to DeMille.
Like hell I'll let you do that!
Unfortunately for you,
I don't really care what
you feel like doing.
I will complete my mission here
and continue living as
a member of DeMille!
That's just wrong!
No matter what the cause!
The duck!
Here, Kokonose, take this!
Sonokata.
I'm entrusting
everything to you now.
Let's arrest Inspector Vega
so we can lock him away forever!
Yeah!
Let's get this over with, Chuta.
Chuta, I'm near my limit here!
Let's end this once and for all!
Here goes, Dolugh!
[yells]
You're done!
Chuta!
Kokonose!
[yells]
[ALL]
Sympathy!
Where'd this power come from?
[ALL yelling]
I won't give up!
Hey! I'm trying to flee!
But, Junior--
This sets a bad
example for the crew!
[VERONICA]
Ah, found ya!
We're elDLIVE.
You're goin' down, guys!
[yells]
At least I'll finally be
liberated from this torture.
Vega, no! No!
And I can finally
be... at peace.
I don't want to lose
anyone else ever again!
Chuta.
But why would you save me?
I am not just gonna
let you die here!
[BOTH] You'll atone for every
bad thing you've done.
Chuta, Misuzu, you all right?
This is Officer
Kokonose reporting.
We're safe and sound.
I see. Nicely done!
[MIMI]
Here ya go!
Freshly baked muffins!
Oh, yeah! Score!
Skaa!
Aw, thank you so much!
They look great!
[chattering]
Everyone's lives are
back to normal now.
It's a good thing that
Vega and his family
have been secured by
elDLIVE, huh, Chuta?
It's all because the Chief
put in a request to HQ.
[MISUZU clears throat]
Kokonose. I, um, I'm so sorry.
About the whole bad smell
thing the other day.
What smell thing?
So then I guess you just weren't
misunderstanding her after all.
Uh, well, now I've
properly apologized,
so if you'll excuse me...
What are those two
whispering about now?
Are they having a super
intense private conversation?
I'm fascinated.
[LOVE]
Mmm, I'm fascinated.
By your flesh.
[VERONICA]
Kopniecie!
[RIGGS]
We being too carefree?
I mean, we aren't even done
with the ship's repairs yet.
Oh, come on. Today's all
about celebrating Chuta.
That's right,
and because Officer Kokonose
arrested Inspector Vega...
...we were in the end
ultimately able to...
...acquire valuable
SPH information
that we can use to take
down DeMille, so--
Man, I didn't know
what we were gonna do
when that virus hit, but I gotta
say, I was pretty worried.
[MCCLANE]
Yeah, I know!
[ALL laughing]
[CHUTA]
Hey, you got a minute?
It feels like we always end up
fighting with each
other, you know?
And never really just talking.
But I wanna thank
you for everything.
I still remember, you told me
that as an officer of elDLIVE,
I could help protect the
Earth from danger.
I think that that was what
inspired me to work so hard.
And yet, as usual,
your actions were reckless,
poorly thought through,
and without anything remotely
resembling strategy.
Even your decision to save
Inspector Vega's life,
while humane, I can't say it
was the right call to make.
That being said,
it is true that everything
worked out all right in the end.
So now, Officer Kokonose,
I suppose I can finally say
that I approve of you
joining elDLIVE.
Wait, finally?
Does that mean
that all this time
you disapproved of me joining?
Good for you, Chuta.
It is not good at all!
[MIMI cries]
[CHUTA]
Huh?
I can't believe
my little Chuta's
talking to a girl
all by himself.
[LAINE, TATEYAN]
Yeah, yeah!
[BOTH scream]
[CHUTA]
Ever since I joined elDLIVE,
so many crazy things
have happened.
There's plenty of stuff that I
still don't fully understand,
but I know that I'll keep
trying as hard as I can.
If that's what it takes to
protect everyone's smiles.