This time, I'm getting
rid of you for good!
[DOLUGH]
Look out, Chuta!
They vanished?
[CHUTA yelps]
What's happening?
Look, your shoulders.
Huh?
Whoa, wings?
This is sweet!
And we can move faster now!
Yes, ordinarily when a
Monitalien switches hosts,
its evolved abilities would
reset back to normal.
But if it goes back to
its old host instead,
the enhanced abilities remain.
This phenomenon is called
Monitalien's Update.
Full disclosure, I'm the one
who came up with that name.
So this is the update?
We can do this!
[VERONICA]
Chief Laine!
What is it?
Can you tell me what the rookie
from Division Two is like?
[LAINE]
Chuta?
Why not find out for yourself
on this joint mission?
Yeah, but I wanna hear
your opinion, Chief.
Well, let's see.
My guess is he wouldn't impress
you no matter what he does.
Even if he's able to
secure Doctor Love
without any problems at all,
you wouldn't appreciate
him as an officer or a man.
Well, that doesn't
sound too promising.
[LAINE]
However...
If you guys run into
some serious trouble,
I think you'll find his
core to be truly reliable.
His core?
I think I might understand
what the chief was
trying to... to say now.
We're able to move so fast now!
It's like her attacks
are barely moving.
[chuckles]
So are you just
gonna keep fleeing?
We can't just keep
running away.
Apparently.
[CHUTA yells]
[DOLUGH] Sewing up won't
work here, Chuta.
Yeah, I know that.
Still, there's gotta
be some way.
I was so scared of
her SPH earlier,
but now, I am not scared at all!
Yeah, I agree.
Hey, Chuta.
In a way, don't you think
Ninotchka's attack
looks like some kinda vegetable?
You think?
[NINOTCHKA]
You may be a little faster now,
but you're still every bit
as weak as before!
Hey, whaddya know,
you're right.
They really do
look like veggies.
Almost like green onions!
[DOLUGH]
Sympathy!
Round Slice!
No, he can't!
Impossible!
I can't believe he was
able to foil my plan.
Well, I have no use
for this girl anymore.
I'll make her bite
her tongue off!
[gasps]
That won't be happening.
Officer Ninotchka?
I extracted the remote
control SPH from her
using this fixed
SPH remover beam.
She'll be fine.
No major injuries.
[sighs]
[CHUTA]
So she's back to normal.
Thank goodness.
Hey, wait a second.
What about the others?
I already treated the blue
shrimp and the Kushutonian girl,
so they're both fine, too.
Wait, when did you...?
There are all sorts of
medical supplies here,
behind the walls and under
the floor of this facility.
If we hadn't been here,
she never would've survived.
Inspector Veronica.
For the record,
I didn't undress her.
Yeah, I know that!
Oh, that's right,
I still need to go
and patch up the
long-haired girl, too.
[DOLUGH] If Doctor Love weren't
here, Veronica would've died.
He seems like a good guy.
Yeah, we all owe him
our lives, although...
...I think there's something
a little off about him.
[LOVE]
By the way,
when I measured the levels
of the remote control SPH
that she had in her body,
I found that she must've
come into contact with
and absorbed it two hours ago.
Any idea how?
Huh? Wait, two hours ago?
But we hadn't even left
the Jeanrenoi-R yet.
Huh?
Does that mean that
whoever infected her
was somewhere within the Bureau?
Well, to use the remote
control SPH on someone,
you do have to come in
contact with a person
and then really
concentrate on them.
But how could they?
[LOVE] There's also the
matter of compatibility,
so not everyone who
was subjected to it
will be controlled.
Which means there's
a possibility
it was used on you, too,
but without any effect.
What? Really?
There are several ways
that it could've happened.
For example, being forced to
look someone in the eyes
at close range for a while.
Look someone in the
eyes for a while?
[BOTH scream]
Could it've been...
Belalugo's interrogator?
So it was when Ninotchka was
being interviewed, huh?
Who would've thought the
interrogator was the bad guy?
Quick, we have to
alert Chief Laine!
[LAINE]
Understood.
Nice work, Chuta. I'll send
a rescue squad right away.
Take good care of everyone.
[LAINE] Deputy Chief Riggs.
This is a Code Nine.
A Code Nine, sir?
A dangerous individual
within the Bureau?
Arrest Belalugo's man, yes,
the interrogator, Dali Lime,
on suspicion of
murder and espionage.
[TONTO]
That guy's the suspect?
Yoyosa! I'll dispatch
a squad to arrest him.
[knocking]
Enter.
[SUBORDINATE B]
Investigator Belalugo,
there's an emergency
message from Chief Laine.
[BELALUGO]
Damn that bra--
[gun fires]
[BELALUGO]
What?
Dali, what are you doing?
[DALI] I'm taking your
authority as an investigator.
[SYSTEM VOICE A]
Investigator-level authority
has been transferred.
You were a foolish,
feckless boss
right up to the end, Belalugo.
Uh, the emergency line
to the investigator
was just cut off forcibly.
[LAINE]
Have any of the squads made it
to the investigator's room yet?
No, but Squad Four should
be there any minute now.
[SPACE COP A]
This is Squad Four. Mayday!
We're being shot at by... Lando!
[laughing]
This is Squad One!
Taro's gone beserk! Send help!
What in the world's going on?
They are all under the spell
of the remote control SPH!
If you have to fight back,
don't hurt them!
[RIGGS]
But, sir--
[LAINE]
I know it won't be easy!
[MCCLANE] Do you really
think that kind of
lackadaisical approach is
going to work, Mister Chief?
Heh-heh.
At this rate, the entire crew's
going to follow Belalugo
straight to Hell.
McClane?
Dali's going to control all
the personnel in the Bureau!
And then he'll kill
everybody off, one by one!
[CHUTA yells]
[DOLUGH] You're the only one
upside down this time.
[CHUTA]
Why me?
I corrected the transfer
algorithm before we left,
but apparently I
forgot to fix yours.
There's trouble!
Some officers are
being controlled
and attacking others, shero!
[CHUTA]
What?
They say they're going
to kill everyone, shero!
Eh, they're just bluffing.
Huh?
Only five percent of those
who've been subjected
to the remote control SPH
are actually susceptible
to its influence.
There's no way they can kill
everyone with just that many.
So then--
Whoever's behind this
has an ulterior motive.
[CHUTA]
But what?
Through his proxies,
the culprit said he wanted
to open the gate to some
treasure with my brain?
I'm afraid right now he's trying
to get ahold of that very gate.
[CHUTA]
A gate?
Doctor Love, what the
heck is this gate?
[LOVE]
Tell me, have you ever heard
of the Taklamakan Project?
[gasps]
[LOVE] We have to hurry.
She's in danger.
[RIGGS] Chief, more personnel
have been brainwashed.
All of the squads are
currently dealing with
at least one member who's
under Dali's control.
[LAINE] He's controlling people
indiscriminately now.
What's he up to?
Uh, Chief.
A door's just been opened using
the investigator's authority.
It's located inside
the detention center.
Detention?
[LAINE] Based on what
McClane said earlier,
I'm guessing Dali
already killed Belalugo.
So he must've stolen the
investigator's authority.
Could his real goal be to--?
If so, then the timing of all of
this would make total sense!
Riggs, Which squad's
closest to detention?
Looks like Squad Three.
They're fighting in
Hall 72 right now.
From their location,
even the fastest route
would take ten minutes.
[LAINE] Damn it!
He's really got us here.
[TONTO]
Chief!
All right, it's time to go.
At last, Great Gate
to the Treasure,
we're finally able to
be alone together.
[DALI] I was going to have
Doctor Love open the gate
using his medical expertise,
but then that
precocious little brat
had to go and get in the way.
Nevertheless, I will
open up this gate,
no matter what it takes.
Which means unleashing
those memories of yours
that have been so
securely locked away.
Not to worry.
Doctor Love isn't the only
scientist around here.
Even if I have to
overmedicate you
or chop up your brain
into tiny little pieces,
I'll get what I'm after!
Leave Sonokata alone!
[DALI grunts]
Oh, great. You again.
Dolugh! Let's block her cell!
So we're gonna do that thing?
I'm not giving up!
Not when I've come this far!
Now! Crochet!
[DALI]
Hm?
Ow. It's hot!
Damn it!
I'll never be able to beat
that kid with my SPH!
He's getting away!
Hold it!
[screams]
[YUTA]
Chief Laine?
I need a spacesuit
right away, you got one?
Uh, where you goin'?
Just out for a little walk.
You'll never catch me!
You won't get away!
[SYSTEM VOICE A]
Identified.
Okay.
It looks like Dali and somebody
else, I'm not sure who yet,
just went through
the emergency exit.
Checking the badge and--
It's Kokonose!
[RIGGS]
Chuta?
Whoa, really?
All right, now he's heading
down Hall 46 in pursuit of Dali.
Damn that Dali.
He must be trying to steal
one of our escape pods.
Yeah, but that sector
is currently--
[DALI laughing]
This is goodbye, you brat!
Hold it!
[SYSTEM VOICE A]
Identified.
[DALI]
So long, kid!
Hey, why am I outside?
[CHUTA]
Whoa, he opened the hatch!
Hold tight!
[DALI] Where in the hell
did the escape pod go?
[CHUTA screams]
You can do it, Dolugh!
The suspect, Dali Lime,
was ejected into space
from Hatch 46,
and is now deceased.
Confirmed cause of
death, suffocation.
What about Chuta?
[LAINE]
Ha-ha. Chuta is fine.
That voice, it's--
[TONTO]
Hey, it's Chief Laine!
[YUTA] Chief, that
spacesuit you wanted.
Did you go out there
to rescue Chuta?
Ah, I understand now.
It was much faster for him to
get there from the outside
with all that commotion
going on inside.
[ALL cheering]
But, Chief, what about
Sonokata's spying charges?
Well, thanks to you
bringing Doctor Love
back here safe and sound,
all that'll be cleared up.
Oh, thank goodness.
Jeez, kid. You really
outdid yourself.
[KIESHI] Excellent work
eliminating the spy
and securing Doctor Love.
Because you found
the true saboteur,
the charges against Sonokata
have all been dropped.
I've cleared her to go
back into the field.
[LAINE]
But, Assistant Commissioner--
This came down from up above.
There's nothing to argue.
Now then, Doctor Love.
I feel like I'm in a dream here.
It's been a while, Kieshi.
You've changed.
Not as much as you have.
[LOVE] Nah, you've
definitely changed more.
In the old days, you were
a stuffy police officer
who wasn't afraid to bite anyone
if you weren't satisfied.
Now you're just spouting
official drivel.
The dirty water that
is being wrung out
of elDLIVE like a giant rag.
You talk to him like that?
My friend, I am just
looking out for you.
Perhaps you should hide
in another safe facility.
[LOVE] If you're gonna try
to force this old man
to wither away in
some dull cage again,
then I'd rather just stay here.
There are many things of
interest to me in this bureau.
For example, there is
the Monitalien organism,
plus one of the subjects
of my project.
You're not thinking
rationally here.
It's too dangerous for
you there, Doctor.
It's a matter of time
before someone else comes
and tries to access Misuzu
Sonokata's memories.
[LOVE] How much longer are you
going to keep up that farce?
I've told you on more
than one occasion
that I can fully restore
Sonokata to a healthy state
and return all of
her memories to her.
The ones who insist on her
remaining a Level 50 patient
are you people.
That isn't our decision
to make. It's Mothers'.
[LOVE] I have no desire
to go against Mothers.
All I'm saying is
that it's safer
if I stay by the girl's side.
I know more about Sonokata's
body than anyone else.
For instance, you
probably aren't aware
of the small but
important effect
Chuta Kokonose has had on
her condition recently.
Wait, Chuta?
[LOVE]
Despite his bland looks,
Kokonose is actually
quite interesting.
I've become convinced that
there must be some reason
that Dolugh needs him.
Very well.
Chief Laine, please, take good
care of Doctor Love now.
Uh, Yoyosa!
[KIESHI]
And assign him some bodyguards.
[LOVE] You mean people
to monitor me, correct?
Come on! Get outta the way!
[DOLUGH]
A lot of people got hurt.
I really wanna ask Doctor
Isaac how Inspector Veronica
and Officer Ninotchka
are doing, but--
[DOLUGH] Looks like they're
pretty busy right now.
[MISUZU]
I heard that both of them
have regained consciousness.
[CHUTA]
Sonokata.
Apparently, it was
thanks to Doctor Love.
They're both asleep right now.
That's great. Thank goodness.
[DOLUGH]
Be careful, Chuta.
Misuzu doesn't know
that she's a subject
in the Taklamakan Project,
or that she was the target here.
Well, at first glance,
it appears that Dali Lime was
plotting this whole time,
trying to find a way he
could use Doctor Love
to unseal Misuzu's memories.
Right around then,
he caught a lucky break
when she let that prisoner out
due to side effects
from her medicine.
So then Dali found
out about that
and put his plan into action.
Now, officially, this
has been filed away
as just attempted
ransom and espionage.
You and I are the only
people here in the Bureau
who know the real story.
Don't tell anyone. Got it?
Especially Misuzu.
Yeah, but, Chief,
what are these memories?
Why did Dali want them?
Sorry, but that's
top secret, kid.
[CHUTA]
In the end,
guess there's still a whole
lot of things I don't know.
But Sonokata's standing here.
And that's good enough for now.
Uh, hey.
Guess you did a pretty good job
with securing Doctor Love.
[CHUTA]
Thanks.
Sorry if I caused you trouble
being suspected of spying.
[CHUTA]
Don't worry about it!
Oh, by the way,
I heard that the
Monitalien was updated.
Yeah, that's right.
He even looks a little
different now, too.
Uh, you're getting
awfully close.
See, look right here!
You see? Check 'em out!
Hope you'll get an
update soon, too.
Frankly, you could use
one a whole lot more
than the Monitalien.
[CHUTA groans]
[growls]
After I just risked my life
fighting to try and save her!
Hold up!
What is it?
You! And your attitude!
Why are you so testy
with me all the time?
I'll be more careful now.
Is that what you want?
No, not at all! You got
something to say, say it!
[MISUZU]
Then I'll be honest with you.
It's your SPH.
Compared to how it was before...
...it's stinky.
[MISUZU]
Stinky, stinky, stinky, stinky.
Excuse me.
There's no way.
She thinks I...
I smell bad?!
[MIMI]
Have a good day!
[CHUTA]
See ya later.
[MIMI] I love you, Chuta!
Watch out for cars now, okay?
Oh, Chuta, what's
going on with you?
He was in the bath for
over an hour yesterday.
And then he used my perfume
without even asking me.
Jeez, I wonder if all boys are
like this when they hit puberty.
[CHIPS]
Morning, chu!
[MISUZU]
Good morning.
Uh. Good morning.
So, uh, there a special reason
why we're meeting at Earth's
local branch today?
There's something
we have to do, chu.
I'm picking up a
very strong odor
coming from Officer
Kokonose, chu.
[MISUZU] It's a perfume
that Earthlings use.
Lady Earthlings.
[grunts]
[DOLUGH]
She figured you out.
Uh, hey, so, Inspector Chips,
just outta curiosity,
has the smell of my SPH changed?
[CHIPS]
Uh?
Your SPH smells the same
as it always does, chu.
[MISUZU clears throat]
[MISUZU] I must've been
mistaken the other day.
Please, don't let it
bother you. I'm sorry.
Mistaken? So then,
you mean I don't stink?
No.
Hey, wait, you're
wearing nose plugs!
They're not nose plugs.
They're nose accessories that
Tykwerians use for rituals.
[CHUTA] But your nose
is still plugged up!
[DOLUGH]
Chuta, look!
Oh, they're here, chu!
[CHUTA]
Huh?
Hey.
Good, I can finally thank
you, Chuta Kokonose.
Yes, thanks for coming to
our rescue the other day!
Uh, what are you
guys doing here?
And why are you wearing
my school's uniform?
We're all part of the team
that's gonna be working
from the same local
branch on Earth, chu.
[CHUTA]
Really?
[CHIPS] Doctor Love will be our
scientific research expert.
And he'll also be able to
keep us all healthy, chu.
Meanwhile, Investigation
Division Five
is in charge of guarding
Doctor Love, chu.
Guarding him?
Yeah, we're here to
keep an eye on him.
That's right.
Doctor Love's a very important
scientist, after all.
Well, you heard the girl.
Looking forward to
working with you.
I don't believe we've met.
Officer Sonokata.
Uh, it's nice to meet you.
[CHUTA]
Huh?
Oh, right.
She doesn't remember anything
about the Taklamakan project,
so for her, this is their
first time meeting.
If Sonokata and Doctor Love
are going to the same
school together now...
All of the students have
gone home for the day.
[MISUZU]
Oh. Yes, Doctor Love.
Now, it's time to begin
today's Taklamakan Project.
Oh, yes, Doctor Love.
So take off your clothes.
[CHUTA]
Damn it, damn it, damn it!
[DOLUGH] Oh, yeah, I'm pretty
sure that's not gonna happen.
I detect something's wrong.
Is he okay?
He's probably just
a little tired.
No, this is normal for him.
All of us going to
the same school?
What's gonna happen now?!
[CHUTA]
You're so fancy, Doctor Love.
[LOVE]
Perhaps, but I'm only interested
in the body's structure
and organs.
I wanna touch raw flesh.
Ninotchka, undress for me.
[NINOTCHKA gasps]
[DOLUGH] Next time on
elDLIVE : "Misuzu's Lie."
[CHUTA]
Wow, that's pretty raw!