Freeze, buddy!
You have the right
to remain silent!
And you have the
right to an attorney!
Veronica!
His true form.
All right, we'll do
it the hard way!
You're up!
Right!
[VERONICA gasps]
Not fair!
We could've brought this
one in without back-up!
[GIRL] I happened to
be in the neighborhood.
No prison cell can hold me!
[LAINE]
All right, that's enough!
The jig is up, Penta.
We have you surrounded!
The Chief's here, too?
That's right. Well, I was
just picking up my lunch.
Just great.
What is going on out there?
[CHUTA]
It was spring.
And for the first time,
I was starting to fit in
with my new class.
In fact, I almost felt normal.
But little did I know...
things were about to get weird.
[CHUTA]
What? You smell something good?
Well, it is spring time.
[TAKEGAWA]
Hm?
[TAKEGAWA clears throat]
Oh, Chuta, who are
you talking to now?
Let's see, I think
my favorite smell
is freshly cleaned clothes after
you take them out of the dryer.
[TAKEGAWA]
Chuta Kokonose!
[CHUTA]
Yes, sir!
[TAKEGAWA] You can't waste
class talking to yourself!
I'm sorry!
[CLASS chuckling]
[STUDENT B] You really like
pushing people's buttons,
don't ya?
[STUDENT C] Yeah, you really
disrespected Takegawa!
Can we please talk about
something else guys?
[STUDENT B chuckles]
Dude, you were the
highlight of that class!
Misuzu, I know Chuta's weird,
but he's also kinda cute, right?
[gasps]
[CHUTA]
Misuzu Sonokata.
I haven't actually ever
talked to her, but..
...I bet that her personality's
really cute, too.
Whoa, dude! You got skills!
[STUDENT C] When it comes to
Home Ec., you're an Iron Chef
crossed with a hotel maid!
Um, thank you?
[STUDENT D]
Excuse me, Kokonose.
Would you consider joining
the cooking club?
We're about to host our
regular kitchen skills
tournament challenge.
What?! You want me?
We couldn't help but
notice your natural talents,
so we thought we'd
extend an invite.
[CHUTA] Thanks, but...
I can't join. Sorry.
[BOTH]
Uh...
Aw, man, I thought
he'd say yes, for sure.
This is why he doesn't
have any friends.
Because he never does anything.
That's not true!
It's not that I don't wanna
do it, it's just that I'm busy.
I have to help my aunt
with her store.
I have responsibilities, guys!
[STUDENT D]
Is he talking to himself?
Oh, God!
[sighs]
[CHUTA]
Believe me,
it's not like I want to talk
to myself all the time.
But there's actually
a very specific reason
why I'm never able to focus
on anything or anyone.
[VOICE] Yeah, you're
a total scatterbrain!
[CHUTA] No, it's
'cause I hear this voice.
[VOICE] Oh, you're always
so negative, Chuta.
It's time you get
confident, stupid!
Would you just leave me alone?
[CHUTA] It shouldn't
surprise you to know
that I'm the only one
who hears the voice.
And that I've been hearing it
for as long as I can remember.
There was a time
when I was little
where I thought
everyone heard it.
But nope, just me.
And because we've always
talked about silly things,
I've never bothered telling
anyone about the voice.
But now that I'm getting older,
it's starting to mess up
my life, more and more.
People catch me
talking to myself,
and rumors spread around
school that I'm a total weirdo.
That's why it's so hard
for me to do stuff.
[VOICE] It's also why
you have no friends.
Shut up!
[CHUTA] There is one other
reason why I'm like this.
[CHUTA]
After that day...
...I swore never to cause
anyone trouble ever again.
[VOICE]
Chuta, I smell oil!
Of course you smell oil,
we were just in cooking class.
[TATEYAN]
Hey, not so tight!
Miss Saotome?
[SAOTOME]
Now, now, Tateyan and Uchida,
what've I told you about
wrestling in the hall like that?
I oughta spank you both.
[UCHIDA chuckles]
No, not that!
[SAOTOME] See me in the
teacher's lounge after school.
[VOICE]
Chuta, it's Blob-Blob!
Come on, I don't like you
out in the hallway, either.
[CHUTA]
Uh, ma'am!
[VOICE]
Blob-Blob, Chuta! Blob-Blob!
I know, I saw her.
[VOICE]
I'm certain it's Blob-Blob!
I'm thinking we should
call her Miss Boing-Boing.
[gasps]
[CHUTA]
Did she hear me?
[CHUTA sighs]
You're a bigger perv than the
other boys at this school.
I hope you die and
I never see you again.
What? You hope I die? But...
[CHUTA] How can something that
looks so sweet sound so mean?
Rejection. I die now.
[VOICE]
Smooth move, Chuta.
[CHUTA] I liked things better
when she didn't know who I was.
[TATEYAN]
Yo!
You got plans after school?
Miss Saotome says she'll
take us to a karaoke bar!
Karaoke with a teacher?
Yeah, are you in?
[CHUTA gasps]
Sorry, I've got work to do.
Your loss!
Yeah.
You're Chuta Kokonose, right?
Gotta say, you sure
are an interesting kid.
Oh, my name's Tateyan.
Well, catch ya later!
Thanks, Tateyan. See ya.
See ya!
[NEWS READER A] A bombshell
story from our bureau in Italy
reports that the Yuzuka
and the mafia have merged.
For the first time in the
history of organized crime,
the Godfather could be Japanese.
[CHUTA]
I live in a muffin shop.
Aunt Mimi, I'm home!
I'm so glad you're back, Chuta!
[VOICE]
Mimi's sure in a good mood.
[CHUTA] So, yeah,
this is my Aunt Mimi.
When it comes to baking
muffins, she's a genius.
But when it comes to
doing anything else,
like chores, not so much.
I kinda need your help.
[CHUTA]
What?
You know how you're
so good at sewing?
Well, all my cleaning
rags are falling apart.
I was wondering if you'd bust
out your needle and thread
and cinch them up for me.
Okay.
That job doesn't sound too hard!
Oh, Chuta, thank you so much!
[VOICE]
You're really earning your keep!
Whatever, it's not a big deal.
[MIMI]
Huh?
Oh, it's nothing.
Hey, Aunt Mimi,
you wanna try the dish
I made today in cooking class?
It's good!
Woohoo! Thanks!
I've been so busy baking,
I totally spaced on lunch!
So good!
Was everything okay
at school today?
What?
I know how when you
talk to yourself,
it can push people away.
No! Nothing happened!
[grunts]
[MIMI]
Are you okay?
Yeah. I'm fine.
[CHUTA] After I lost my parents,
Aunt Mimi raised me on her own.
She knows me better than
anyone, which, of course,
means I can't really hide
anything from her.
[VOICE]
I think someone's here.
I hope you die and
I never see you again.
Boy, she really enjoys
throwing salt in the wound.
I guess every rose
does have its thorns.
[VOICE]
Chuta, someone's here!
But I don't care
how mean she is.
She's still the cutest
girl I've ever seen!
[MALE VOICE] Particle changes
in the target confirmed.
We are go for transfer!
[VOICE]
Ah! Why's it so bright?
--[VOICE] Too bright!
--What? What's happening?
[VOICE]
Chuta, what is this?
Your guess is as good as mine!
Ow. That hurt.
[VOICE]
Where are we?
Chuta! We're in a
completely different place!
[door opens]
[CHUTA]
Uh?
What is this place?
Am I dreaming or what?
Definitely not the muffin shop.
[VOICE] I think there's
something over there.
Chuta, go look over there!
All right, already.
Shut up and...
What's wrong with him? Why's
he talking to himself so much?
Must've hit his head
too hard on the landing.
Constantly talking to
oneself is not attributed
to normal Earthling behavior.
Yeah, and the Earthlings
we've worked with
don't do it anywhere near
as much as this boy.
[VOICE]
Go! Go through the door!
[gasps]
[yelps]
[VOICE]
Cats? Chicks? Triangles?
They look suspicious, Chuta.
Maybe it's an
anime con? Cosplay?
[LAINE] Chuta Kokonose,
just the boy I wanted to see!
Welcome to the
elDLIVE Space Police!
[SPACE POLICE]
Yoyosa!
What? elDLIVE? Space Police?
That's right. I'm Laine Brick.
And I'm the chief of this solar
system's elDLIVE Bureau.
[SPACE EXEC A] Of all the
billions of Earthlings,
why was this boy chosen to join
an elite group like elDLIVE?
[SPACE EXEC B] Yes, judging
from the data we've seen,
nothing indicates he has special
talent or even character.
Gentlemen, if I may.
He was chosen
straight by Mothers.
Wait, what? I was chosen?
[LAINE]
That's right.
We at elDLIVE recruit
any and all beings
who show the potential to become
great Space Police officers.
Across the universe is a vast,
decentralized super-computer
called Mothers.
And in her infinite wisdom,
Mothers has picked you
to join us, Chuta.
Hey, now wait a second!
I'm not just going to join
the "Space Police."
How do I even know
this is all real?
Oh, this elDLIVE Bureau
is real, I assure you.
It's the Jeanrenoi-R!
The who-what?
Yeah.
I know it's a lot to take in
so maybe I should show you?
Hey, Riggs, Tonto, come here.
[BOTH]
Yoyosa!
[CHUTA]
Huh?!
Subject loaded to ejection
block and ready for exit!
Wait, stop! Let me outta here!
Good? Launch away!
[YUTA]
Yoyosa!
[VOICE] The hatch is
opening. It's opening!
[CHUTA]
Eh? Oh, no.
[VOICE] Turn-around, Chuta!
Something's behind us!
It's huge! It's Earth!
[CHUTA]
I hate the Space Police!
Oh, wow.
[LAINE]
Turn around to get a good view
of your local elDLIVE Bureau!
[CHUTA]
The Bureau's a space ship?!
[VOICE] It can't be!
That's just a special effect!
[MELIES chuckles]
Earthlings have
such sloppy form.
Ah! A floating head!
[VOICE]
That looks like a moon!
[MARLY]
Melies, don't scare him.
You can hold my hand
if you're scared.
[CHUTA]
Which one? You have eight!
[VOICE]
I count ten.
[LAINE] There are as many
different life forms
as there are stars
in the cosmos.
And we serve them all.
To protect and maintain order
cross the entire universe!
That is the mission
we strive for
as members of Space
Police elDLIVE!
He's got a way with words.
Coming from anyone else,
it would sound so cheesy.
[LAINE]
Anyway, kid,
all you have to do is pass
the qualifying exam,
and you'll be the latest member
of our special family!
What?! A member?!
Hold on, I haven't expressed
any interest in joining you!
Ha! They all say that.
Let's start the test!
Come on, don't I have a choice?
[VOICE]
Stop whining, Chuta!
Becoming a Space Policeman
sounds like a blast.
Just take the test!
Hey, shut up! I'm through
listening to you!
Man, he really does
talk to himself a lot.
[CHUTA]
Um, so...
[LAINE]
Hm?
[CHUTA]
...I don't wanna do it.
[sighs]
Come on, kid, the
exam isn't that hard.
I said no.
Okay. This isn't good.
Well, what are we gonna
tell the home office?
I know!
What if by some coincidence
we suffered a "wink-wink"
mechanical failure
with life support?
Oh. I gotcha.
Like there's a terrible accident
where the oxygen runs
out of his space suit
and Chuta's unable to
take the qualifying exam
and we're off the hook
with the bosses!
[CHUTA] You know I can hear
everything you're saying!
I do not agree with this.
As you've no doubt seen from
his habit of talking to himself,
he suffers from
delusions...
[VOICE]
I know this voice.
[GIRL] ...constantly indulges
them, no matter where he is.
His cringe-factor is ten
times higher than average
of other middle schoolers
in his country.
Sooner or later,
he'll be subject
to the Prefectural Ordinance
of Juvenile Protection.
Simply put, he's not
worth the trouble.
Listen, lady, I don't
know who you are,
but I'm sick of you
babbling about me!
Babbling?
I'm gonna show you
who's worth the trouble.
When I pass your stupid exam
with the highest score
you've ever seen!
Great! That's the
right call, kid!
I'll start the
paperwork right away!
[TONTO]
And... that's that!
Uh, thanks.
Look, I know when I was out
there, I said I'd do this, but--
[VOICE] Don't back
out now! It'll be fun!
[CHUTA]
Uh.
There's a C-rank criminal
from planet Chabrol
hiding out on Earth,
and your mission is to arrest
him for us with these.
Do all that and
you pass the test.
Handcuffs? Is this
thing dangerous?
[LAINE]
Hmm.
Well, it's a
carnivorous predator,
so there's a not-zero chance
you might be eaten alive.
[CHUTA]
What?!
Sheronimo!
All set, Chief!
SPH Check, now commencing!
[CHUTA] Wait! You didn't even
tell me where I was going yet!
[VOICE]
It's that light!
Can I take a written test?
[VOICE]
Not again!
Owie!
Where am I?
[VOICE] Looks like the third
block of Keiki Town.
[CHUTA]
Yeah. Right by my house!
Wait, the space
criminal lives near me?
[VOICE] I think it's pretty
funny that all this time
there's been an alien
right under your nose.
It's not funny!
[VOICE] Okay, okay.
Let's just find the alien!
I don't think it's
gonna be that easy.
Where do I start?
I mean, everyone
I see around here
looks like they could be
an alien in disguise.
Huh.
Of all the Earthlings, I wonder
why Mothers picked him.
Oh, wow.
Harry, find something?
Data on Chuta Kokonose.
Sseen some strange thermographic
readings in my day,
but never like this on
an Earthling before.
'Kay, how strange?
This concentration here is
slightly higher than the rest.
And it's moving all
around his body.
[LAINE]
Hm.
[sighs]
Maybe this is just a test
and there isn't an alien here.
[VOICE]
Oil! Chuta, I smell oil again!
Sorry, I don't smell anything.
[SAOTOME]
Oh, look, it's Mr. Kokonose.
Oh, hey, Chuta!
[CHUTA]
Uh, hey, guys.
[VOICE]
Ah! Blob-Blob!
[CHUTA]
So you're done with karaoke?
I'm just walking Tateyan home
to make sure he doesn't
get into trouble.
Yeah, trouble.
Yeah. Sure. Great.
[VOICE] It's Blob-Blob
who smells like oil!
How many times do I have to
say she doesn't smell like oil?
[SAOTOME gasps]
Young man, are you saying
that I have B.O.?
Oh, no. Of course not.
Miss Saotome smells like roses
blooming after a spring shower!
Her smell?
That might have something
to do with her SPH.
No way, Chief.
The science is clear
that sensing SPH
is physically impossible
for Earthlings.
[VOICE] Chuta, listen: The oil
smell is coming from Blob-Blob.
It's the only answer
that makes sense!
For the last time,
she doesn't smell bad,
and certainly not like oil!
And stop calling
her "Blob-Blob,"
it only gets me in trouble.
Blob-Blob?
Did you really just call
a teacher "Blob-Blob"?
Miss Saotome?
Uh-oh.
[SAOTOME] If only you
idiots knew how much
I hate being called Blob-Blob.
In fact, the only thing
that bothers me more...
...is going so
long without food!
[BOTH scream]
Chabrolian detected, Chief!
[MCCLANE] Sounds like Chuta
found our criminal!
Well.
Oh, no! How dare you expose me!
[VOICE] See? She really was
a Blob-Blob! I was right!
If I were you, I'd add another
blob. That thing's big!
Don't be so mean!
I'm standing right here!
Wha--? That's an elDLIVE Badge!
Well, you're never
gonna bring me in!
'Cause if you take one step
closer, I'll kill this brat!
[TATEYAN squeals]
Tateyan!
Help! Don't let
him eat me, Chuta!
You have to save me, Chuta!
[GUCCHI]
Don't let me fall!
I'll save you!
[VOICE]
The rock on the right!
Got it!
[VOICE]
No, that one's not safe!
[gasps]
[ALL screaming]
Something bad's gonna
happen, I know it!
[VOICE]
Chuta, you always say that.
You're the problem!
And all your stupid talking
in my head has ever done
is turn me into a
useless crazy person!
I can't become a
space policeman!
Now that you realize you
can't win, get lost, elDLIVE!
No, don't leave me, Chuta!
Please, you're the only
one who can save me.
I haven't even
kissed a girl yet!
Chuta!
He is right. It's all up to me.
You scream too much!
[TATEYAN groaning]
Tateyan!
[VOICE]
Bad news, Chuta.
If we don't do something,
Blob-Blob will kill
all three of us!
Come on, kid.
[TATEYAN choking]
[CHUTA] For most of my life I've
felt like if I do anything good,
something bad will
always happen.
That's why when people get
close, I push them away.
But now...
Oh, my name's Tateyan.
Well, catch ya later!
[CHUTA] This is different,
it isn't about me anymore.
He needs my help.
[VOICE] We can fall back
and save ourselves.
No, we're staying.
There's gotta be a way!
[VOICE]
Chuta?
You're a part of me
and I need your help!
Come on, if we think together,
we can save Tateyan!
[VOICE]
What did you say, Chuta?
Stop playing dumb and help
me come up with a plan!
I'm the only one who can help.
Tateyan! I'll save you!
[VOICE]
I'm part of you?
This is strange, Chuta. I've
never had this feeling before.
Chief, I'm seeing a rapid
increase in Chuta's SPH count.
[LAINE]
Uh?
Stop it! Let Tateyan go!
Oh, look, I can make
his head pop off!
Let go!
Squeezy-squeeze!
Stop it!
[VOICE]
Sympathy!
[CHUTA]
Huh?
[SAOTOME screams]
[CHUTA gasps]
It's been a while since
someone activated
my Symbiotic Technique!
[CHUTA]
What?
[CHUTA yelps]
What-What the heck?!
[LAINE]
The symbol on its forehead
is that of the Lost Griffith!
And if it's operating on Earth,
that's a sure sign that we're
dealing with... a Monitalien!
They're a kind of observer.
Special organisms scattered
across the universe
on countless planets.
The people of
Griffith created them
over four billion years ago.
[KIESHI]
Hm...
What's with the
weird look, Chuta?
No way!
You can see me?
You're the voice? You mean
all this time it's been you?
I'll have to explain it later.
The Blob-Blob's waking up!
I don't know where that
energy blast came from,
but I'm sure gonna
make you pay for it!
[CHUTA screams]
You look tasty!
No way.
Use your imagination!
All you have to do is
picture an attack for us
and it'll happen for real!
Okay.
[SAOTOME]
Bon appetit!
[roars]
Uh, Voice?
Look at Blob-Blob's body
and think about how
we can defeat it.
[CHUTA]
Huh?
Its body?
Well, it's flabby and
loose like old fabric.
What if we cinch him into a ball
so he's not a danger anymore?
[VOICe]
Sympathy!
Here goes!
[SAOTOME]
Hey! I can't breathe!
[CHUTA]
Huh?
And don't forget the handcuffs!
Uh, now that we got that thing,
what the heck are you?
So the newest member of
elDLIVE's an Earthling
who's able to tap the
power of a Monitalien.
Heh.
I like.
[CHUTA]
Ow!
[LAINE]
Chuta Kokonose!
Congratulations, kid,
you passed the entrance exam.
I passed? For real?
[GIRL]
I'm still against this.
[GIRL grunts]
Wait, you're her?
Misuzu is a Space Cop?
[DOLUGH] Our sewing attack
worked pretty well.
[CHUTA]
Yeah!
[LAINE] It worked, but you need
to come up with a better move.
[CHUTA]
Hey, I think sewing's cool!
[LAINE]
Eh.
[CHUTA]
Aw.
[DOLUGH] Next time on elDLIVE :
"Super Cool Space Girl"!
[LAINE] By the way, could you
fix a hole in one of my socks?