Sorry to barge in when
you're having so much fun.
I'm looking for an old geezer
by the name of Doctor
Taklamakan Strangelove.
If he doesn't show himself,
then I'll just have to--
[LOVE]
Hold it!
I'm right here. I am
Doctor Love, 'kay?
[chuckles]
How many body doubles
do you think I've
tracked down so far?
But not to worry, I can tell
if you're the real doctor or
just a decoy using my SPH.
Just how long are you
going to play dumb?
I don't know.
I have no idea what
you're talking about.
Don't be absurd!
This footage was
taken right before
the convicted murderer Dragline
escaped from police custody.
As you can see,
we have video,
captured with a special camera
that shows you cutting through
the grid at the detention center
to break him out.
So you can't talk
your way out of this!
Now tell me what
you're planning!
I don't know. I... don't know.
Think I'll fall for that?
[SUBORDINATE A] She really
has lost consciousness, sir.
[BELALUGO] Ugh. What about
the lie-detector SPH?
[SUBORDINATE A]
We couldn't detect anything.
She's a spy, damn it!
And I'll get her to confess,
whatever it takes.
Next in line, make your way
to Interrogation Room Six.
We haven't even finished
fixing Jeanrenoi-R
from the damage caused
by the DeMille attack.
We don't need this now.
There's nothing we can do.
They think that
Sonokata's a suspect.
Suspect? She's guilty!
There's footage of her
letting a murderer escape
that was captured
with our cameras!
Of course the girl's a spy!
Misuzu hasn't confessed, chu!
That doesn't change the fact
that there's video proof!
For all we know, she might've
been spying on all of us, too.
[CHIPS]
There's no way, chu!
I've been with Misuzu since
she joined the bureau,
so I would know, chu!
Both your naïve way of thinking
and your SPH reek
of a small child!
Yeah, well, your attitude reeks
just as bad as your afro!
[BOTH]
What gives?
[TONTO]
That's enough outta you two.
[DOLUGH] So do you think
Misuzu's a spy, Chuta?
No, absolutely not!
[DOLUGH] Even though she
was caught on camera?
Even so, I still trust Sonokata.
Uh, for the same reason
that Chips does.
Yeah, but unlike Chips,
you haven't known Misuzu for
very long, have you, Chuta?
Well, uh, yeah, but--
Say, you're really being pushy.
Do you want Sonokata
to be found guilty?
Gosh, no!
I just wanna know why you're
so eager to trust her,
even if it means averting
your eyes from the truth.
I am not averting my
eyes from the truth.
[SUBORDINATE C] Next up
to the interrogation room.
Yes, sir.
[SUBORDINATE A] She's developed
a fever over the past two hours.
I'm afraid the cause of
it is still unknown.
[BELALUGO] Well, fix it!
And straighten her up!
What do you want, huh?
Investigator Belalugo
is busy right now.
Then I'll just wait
here till he's done.
If words aren't enough
to get through to you--
[growling]
You little--
You leave me no choice.
Ouch! That one's tough.
[door opens]
[BELALUGO grunts]
Well, it's Laine Brick.
One of your charming henchmen
tried to get rid of me
by threatening to use force,
so sadly I had to
resort to self-defense.
And if you don't believe me,
then by all means,
check the special camera
footage that you're so fond of.
What do you want, Brick?
[LAINE]
As chief of this Bureau,
I request an interview
with Officer Sonokata.
Request denied!
I'm under no obligation
to let you see her.
Hmph. Good day.
I'm guessing Misuzu
has a high fever by now.
And if a suspect becomes
ill during interrogation,
they should be allowed
to have access
to their personal physician.
Personal physician?
But you know the rules, Brick.
It's only reserved for sick
people who are above Level 50.
Yes, and Misuzu is one that
falls into that category.
She's a test subject in
the Taklamakan Project.
I think you know
what that means.
You're serious?
So you'll allow me to send
in her personal physician
and an assistant to treat her?
[BELALUGO grunts]
Very well. However, I won't
be going easy on her.
[TONTO]
Chief!
There's an emergency message for
you from Superintendent Kieshi.
Copy. Be right there.
[DALI] So that's the only
conversation you had
with Officer Sonokata
while the two of you
were at the detention center?
[CHUTA]
Yeah.
And you swear that everything
you've said to me here today
is the truth?
[CHUTA]
Again with the "truth."
Sheesh, everyone keeps going on
and on about "the truth."
Even Dolugh accused me of
ignoring the truth earlier.
[DOLUGH]
Chuta, he's asking a question.
Uh.
[DALI] Look into my eyes
and answer me!
[CHUTA screams]
Yes. Yes, sir!
[DALI]
All right, then. Next.
[sighs]
[DOLUGH] Wow. You were really
lost in thought earlier.
[CHUTA] Yeah and it was
your fault for askin' me
all about Sonokata right
before that interrogation.
Uh?
[BOTH yelp]
[VERONICA]
Hey, watch it!
What's wrong with you? You
could've broken my horn off!
Your horn?
And hey, wait a second, you're
the one who bumped into me here.
[VERONICA]
Well, I don't remember
because I'm a little out
of it from just waking up!
[CHUTA] What? She's making it
sound like that's my fault!
[NINOTCHKA]
Please forgive her.
She's suffering from jetlag.
Are you all right there?
Oh, I'm okay, really.
But thank you.
[CHUTA] Hmm, both of those
girls look to be about my age.
[ISAAC]
Chuta!
You got a second?
Uh, sure.
Wait, this is...
[CHUTA] I still don't
believe that Sonokata
let that Dragline guy
escape the other day.
No matter what anyone says.
Hurry up.
[CHUTA]
Sonokata!
Not good.
Her memories are beginning
to get muddled.
Hang in there, Misuzu.
What's going on with Sonokata?
Just what did they do to her?
[ISAAC]
They didn't do anything to her.
It's just her medicine
wearin' off.
[CHUTA]
Medicine?
You know.
Remember when Misuzu
came to get her kit
and talked about
how it helped her
adapt to the ship's environment?
[DOLUGH] Those were the pills
she got from sickbay.
Well, Misuzu doesn't know it,
but it's really a drug designed
to help manage the side effects
of a top-secret project.
Very hush-hush.
Side effects?
Chuta, what I'm
about to tell you
is somethin' that only the
chief, Chips, and I know about.
A while ago, Misuzu was forced
to undergo a medical procedure.
As a result of this, her body's
balance was destroyed
and she lost six months'
worth of memories.
[CHUTA]
What?
[ISAAC] An SPH-producing
organ was transplanted
from another individual
and put into Misuzu.
After that, her
personality changed.
This endeavor was known
as the Taklamakan Project.
But the entire project
ended in failure.
And most of those who
underwent the operation
either lost their lives or
had their bodies inflicted
with some sort of severe defect.
For her, that meant
losing all memory
related to the experiment.
And becoming unable to survive
without taking that medication
and now she's completely
dependent on it.
But why was she forced to
undergo something like that?
I don't have the answer to that.
'Cause it's top secret.
[CHUTA] So then why did
you tell me all this?
Why do you think?
I told you because you're now in
a position to protect Misuzu.
Protect... Sonokata?
Me?
The chief knows I was plannin'
to tell you all about this.
And he's onboard with it.
So now what?
Listen up, Second Division.
Got a mission for you.
This scientist is currently
residing on Earth.
I need you to bring
him back here.
Doctor Love.
One of the greatest scientists
in the whole universe.
Old acquaintance of mine.
He's 500 years old
and a total weirdo.
Five hundred?
Thing is, Doctor Love hates
people getting in his way,
so up till, now we've left
him alone without security.
But four of his
five body doubles
have turned up dead
in recent days.
[BOTH scream]
With things becoming
this dangerous,
can't maintain the status quo.
elDLIVE HQ ordered us to provide
protection for the doctor.
Uh, yeah, but, sir--
Right now I'm worried
about Misuzu, chu.
Are you worried, too?
Yes.
[LAINE] Don't let your personal
feelings get in the way!
Right! I'm sorry, sir!
Though I get what
you're going through.
I mean, ever since
Misuzu was arrested,
I've been binge-eating
dumplings.
[CHUTA grunts]
Now, this is completely
coincidental,
but as a bonus, this mission
could very well end up
being a way for us
to save Misuzu.
[BOTH]
Huh?
Ah, of course.
You see, Doctor Love's
full name is...
...Doctor Taklamakan
Strangelove.
He's the one who conceived
of the Taklamakan Project
I was telling you about earlier.
Yeah, okay, but what
does all that have to do
with saving Misuzu, chu?
[LAINE] Doctor Isaac and
I think the activity
that led to Misuzu
being accused of spying
might've been caused
by a side effect
of the medicine she's taking.
It's unconfirmed,
but similar incidents
have been reported in the past.
Others who've taken
this medicine
have apparently done things
they don't remember doin'.
Doctor Love created
the medicine,
so if we can get him to testify
that Misuzu cutting through the
grid was a just side effect,
this'll be deemed an accident
and she can go free.
Oh, I get it, chu.
Uh, I don't think I
followed all of that.
[DOLUGH]
I did!
But if we bring
back Doctor Love,
then that'll help us save
Sonokata, right?
So you'll go?
[BOTH]
Yoyosa!
[LAINE] You'll be working
with the Fifth Division
on this mission.
I've already given the
details to their leader.
[CHIPS]
We got transferred upside down.
[CHUTA] He did it again.
Come on, Sheronimo!
I'll let him off
the hook this time
because I'm in a good mood, chu.
We just gotta bring
Doctor Love back
and Misuzu can be
declared innocent, chu!
Ha-ha! That's true.
You see, Dolugh? It turns
out I was right all along.
I told you Sonokata
wasn't a spy.
Oh, but I never
said that she was.
Huh?
I just wanted to know
why you trusted Misuzu
when you didn't have
anything to back it up.
Sheesh, you're still
going on about that?
[CHIPS] Hey, I wanna be part of
this conversation, too, chu!
But I can't hear the
Monitalien! No fair, chu!
[BOTH grunt]
Freeze right there!
Don't move.
Hey, what're you doing?
[VERONICA]
Oh, it's you guys.
[NINOTCHKA]
Forgive our rude greeting,
Assistant Inspector Chips.
Oh, it's you!
We've been waiting here for you.
We're from Investigations
Division Five
and we'll be working with
you on this mission.
[ISAAC laughs]
Man, talk about
clever calculations.
Yes, but still...
What's the matter?
It's Misuzu's arrest and
Doctor Love's decoys.
The timing feels a
little too convenient.
[CHUTA gasps]
I ran into you after
my interrogation!
Yeah, yeah, well,
that was my bad, okay?
There, see, I apologized!
Now it's your turn!
So what're you waiting for?
[CHUTA]
Huh?!
Let me introduce you, chu.
This is Division Five's--
[VERONICA] Assistant Inspector
Veronica Borowczyk,
leader of the Fifth Division.
Okay, well, over to my right--
[VERONICA] Officer Nina
Mikhailovna Pavlova.
But you can call me Ninotchka.
Told you, chu!
Oh, and my name's--
[VERONICA]
Officer Chuta Kokonose.
[CHUTA]
Huh?
The new guy who supposedly
arrested a C-rank
during his entrance exam.
The one they call
"Super Rookie."
Uhh...
Oh, boy, you're famous, Chuta.
[gasps]
It's so cute!
Are you the Monitalien
everyone's talking about?
[CHUTA screams]
Whoa, what's wrong
with you, Dolugh?
That's the first time a
stranger's touched me!
Oh, I'm so sorry.
Still, I gotta say,
you sure do seem to be every bit
as mind-numbingly boring a guy
as all the rumors say.
[CHUTA, DOLOUGH gasp]
There are rumors?
Why would you ever say that?
What? I'm just saying
what's on my mind.
I swear, she's really a
nice person deep down.
Very deep down.
She just speaks her mind a
little too freely, that's all.
For what it's worth, I certainly
don't think you're boring.
Oh, right, I forgot
that you're into
frail and dorky boys like him.
[NINOTCHKA]
Veronica!
[CHUTA]
Frail? Dorky?
Now what's Misuzu
gotten herself into?
She is so dumb,
it's not even funny.
Oh, don't mind Veronica.
This is just her unique
way of showing affection.
See, the three of us girls all
joined elDLIVE at the same time.
So, we're close enough to
really let each other have it.
If that were true, Misuzu and
I'd be fighting to the death.
[CHUTA]
So they're our age.
Well, let's get to work.
If we team up, I'll be able
to see you in action
and will instantly know whether
you really are a super rookie,
or if that's all just hype.
Huh?
And away we go!
[DOLUGH, CHIPS]
Yeah!
[VERONICA] We're supposed to
make contact with Doctor Love
in that restaurant right there.
But keep your guard up,
because we might not be the
only ones looking for him.
Okay, Kokonose, go over
there and check it out.
Uh? Uh, yoyosa!
You're too conspicuous!
Why can't you just
use your Monitalien
to peek inside or something?
[DOLUGH]
Now there's an idea.
[VERONICA] Though most officers
would just use one of these.
'Kay, all clear.
We are a go.
[CHUTA] You know, you coulda
just done that yourself
from the start, you demon!
[NINOTCHKA]
Are you all right?
Here, you can use my
handkerchief, if you want.
Oh, thanks, but I have my own.
Wow, it's so nice
and crisply ironed.
Your mom really loves you.
Nah, I did that.
[NINOTCHKA gasps]
That's amazing!
[giggles]
[CHUTA]
But this one, she's an angel!
[NEWS ANCHOR A]
Next up, we bring you
a remarkable story
from overseas...
Quit gawking, okay.
You won't spot Doctor Love
'cause he's not here.
[CHUTA]
Huh?
Did you really think he'd
just be sipping a cup of tea
while his life's in danger?
Obviously he'd send someone.
[CONCIERGE]
Welcome.
Table for three, miss?
[VERONICA giggles]
Pardon me!
My grandpa left his hat.
It's a grey fedora.
Ah, I see, miss.
You must be one of our
special customers then.
Grandpa?
I know. That was a
secret code, Chuta.
Oh, like when they ask,
"What's the password?"
in movies.
Pity.
If only you had showed
up a little sooner,
things wouldn't
have come to this.
[ALL gasp]
[CHUTA yelps]
Is he dead?
Hey, what's going on here?
Welcome, elDLIVE.
I'm glad to see you.
Because if you are around,
that means the real Doctor Love
must be somewhere very close by.
So you're the monster
who's been killing off all his
body doubles, aren't you?
Please, Officer Chips,
alert the Jeanrenoi-R!
[CHIPS]
You got it, chu.
Not so fast.
Sorry, your SPH comms are
not going to work in here,
so you won't be able to
ask your friends for help.
[ALL gasp]
And now it's my turn to
ask you a few questions.
You know where Doctor
Love is, don't you?
[DOLUGH] This is bad, Chuta!
We're surrounded!
[VERONICA]
Very well.
If it's a fight you want,
then it's a fight you'll get!
[VERONICA]
SPH...
[yells]
[VERONICA]
...Kopniecie!
Fire!
Now SPH...
...brót akcja!
All right!
Well, that's elDLIVE for you.
But what if I were to tell you
they were innocent civilians?
Say, what was I just doing?
Where am I?
Man, I'm so confused.
You mean...?
Were all of those poor
people hypnotized?
[IRWIN]
By the way...
If that device detonates,
this whole restaurant
will be blown to pieces.
[IRWIN]
Now, where is Doctor Love?
We don't know.
If you don't answer
me truthfully,
everyone in here is
going to go boom.
Veronica.
He's underneath this place.
I swear, that's all I know!
Ah, I see. Down there, huh?
Oh well, then I guess I'll just
have to blow up this
joint after all.
[ALL gasp]
So long, boys and girls.
Stop the bomb, chu!
I'd love to, but how?
Chuta! I know!
I saw a bomb squad freeze
an explosive on TV once
while you were sleeping!
Hey, wait, who said
you could do that?
I don't think now's
the time, Chuta.
[CHUTA] Okay, the same move as
that time we froze the gum off.
[DOLUGH]
Sympathy!
[CHUTA]
Freezing Bomb Stop!
All right, that delayed
the explosion for a bit
and bought us some time!
Everyone! Get behind me! Now!
Careful!
[NINOTCHKA]
I know.
[CHIPS]
Everyone's okay, chu.
[VERONICA] Now all of you
hurry up and get somewhere safe!
Just now... was that your SPH?
Oh, yeah.
It was pretty, um, awesome!
So, um, did you...
...uh, see anything?
Huh?! No, uh... Nothing.
Hey, Officer Kokonose!
All of this was your
fault, you know that?
If you had just frozen the
bomb right at the start,
then he wouldn't have found
out where Doctor Love was,
and this place would've
never been blown up!
My verdict, you are
definitely no super rookie.
Just dead weight.
Just dead weight?
Oh, that hurts me, too.
Now that's going too far.
He'll never learn if
I don't spell it out.
I'm dead weight?
Oh, no! Chuta's confidence
is melting away!
So you're all set
to escape now, huh?
[ALL gasp]
[IRWIN] It's him! I finally
get to meet the real deal!
[gasps]
[NINOTCHKA]
Oh, no!
[gasps]
[NINOTCHKA]
How awful!
[MAN]
So much noise.
Someone's there!
You need the old geezer
for something?
Sorry, but... you
should've come sooner.
[CHUTA]
Oh, Inspector Veronica.
[VERONICA] What am I gonna do?
I made a mess in my sleep again.
[CHUTA]
Wait, you wet the bed?
[VERONICA]
As if!
No, my horn tore a hole in the
mattress when I rolled over!
[DOLUGH]
Next time on elDLIVE :
"Something to Believe
In: Part Two."
[CHUTA]
Way to be misleading!