[MARUKOBI]
My name's Ichiro Marukobi.
[MARUKOBI] They say there are
three other people in the world
who look just like you,
but in my case,
it's a whole lot more than that.
Please come again.
[BOYS laughing]
[MARUKOBI] Guess I must
be special or something.
Not that it's done me
any good up till now.
[MELPLEIAN A]
Sorry you had to wait.
Uh, sorry, do I know you?
Oh, stop kidding
around, you kidder.
Now, let's hurry up and go.
We're gonna be late.
[MARUKOBI]
Huh? Go where? Wait!
Hold on! I think you
have the wrong guy!
[MELPLEIAN B]
Do you know how late you are?
[MELPLEIAN A]
I'm so sorry!
[MELPLEIAN C] I thought
you weren't gonna come.
Well, of course she came.
How could she not?
[MELPLEIANS laughing]
[MARUKOBI]
Crap! What's going on?
Skaa!
Now then, let's get started...
with this mixer!
[MARUKOBI]
M-M-Mixer?!
[MISUZU]
This SPH...
...reminds me of playing in
a grassy field as a child.
It's like a gentle scent.
One that I love.
It feels so warm and
refreshing to me.
[ISAAC]
Huh.
Well, you're all clear.
Now then, is there anything
else bothering you today?
Not really.
For example,
is there some SPH that never
caught your attention before,
but now, it suddenly just
makes you uncomfortable?
[gasps]
Meaning, do any of
them have a bad scent?
Like, say, Officer
Kokonose's SPH?
How'd you--?
I got him to confess.
See, I've noticed that his SPH's
accuracy and intensity
have increased.
It seems Chuta must have
matured a little after updating.
[MISUZU] It's fine. I can
endure Officer Kokonose's SPH.
It doesn't affect my work.
Calm down now.
We're not tryin' to take your
job away here, Misuzu.
[MISUZU]
But--
Just tell us honestly
what happened.
I'm quite fascinated.
Okay, well, when Officer
Kokonose first showed
the updated Monitalien to me,
there was something very strong
and foul about his SPH.
The smell was so powerful,
it went up my nose and felt like
my brain was going to split.
It's difficult now for me to
even stand in front of him
without wearing nose plugs.
Ah, now I see.
I may've narrowed down
the possible causes.
Here, try this.
It's a hairpin-type SPH curtain.
You can cut down on a specific
SPH just by wearing it.
What's the problem?
Uh, does it come
in another design?
This isn't my style.
It's too childish.
[grumbles]
[sighs]
[VERONICA]
Misuzu?
What's that in your hair?
[MISUZU]
Oh. Nothing.
Just a new hairpin, that's all.
Oh, I see.
So that's the kind of thing
that you're into, is it?
Got a problem with that?
Not really. It's just
unlike you to be so girly.
Honestly, it looks a
little bit childish.
[MISUZU growls]
Uh, well, I don't think
it's really all that weird.
I mean, I totally get wanting
to change up your hairstyle
like that every now and then.
It's just too bad
that my battle suit
is so embarrassingly revealing.
If I were to cut my hair any,
I don't think there'd be
enough left to cover my body.
Well, come to think of it,
Officer Kokonose sure saw
a lot of you the other day.
[whining]
[VERONICA]
Well, time for work!
[VIRGIL] So you had
a run-in with a thief?
Was there anything
valuable in your bag, sir?
So it was an
attempted kidnapping?
[JAECKINIAN A]
I was groped by a groper!
Please, calm down, ma'am.
Somebody poked my elbow!
For my kind, elbows are
as intimate as boobs are
to you Earthlings!
Did you say boobies?
'Kay, um, guess I'll make a
composite sketch of the suspect?
I don't want you!
I'd rather have this
handsome fella over here.
[CHUTA]
Huh?
That's right. I got this, chu!
[sighs]
[DOLUGH] Chuta!
Misuzu's looking over here.
Oh, good morning.
Uh, good morning.
[DOLUGH] Hey, look! She's not
wearing her nose plugs!
Sonokata, your nose
plugs. But my smell.
[MISUZU]
What about it?
Huh? Well, uh...
The nose plugs were
just an accessory.
And they had nothing
to do with your SPH.
[CHUTA] Seriously?!
So I just had the wrong idea?
You mean I don't stink?
Right.
For real? Nah.
Yes.
[CHUTA] So then all this time
I've been worried for nothing?!
What's that? I've never
seen you wear hair clips.
Yes, I know it's childish!
[CHUTA]
Huh?
I mean, I'm just not
really that fond of it.
Then, why are you wearing
it if you don't like it?
[MISUZU]
Um... For my appearance.
Wait, what?
[MISUZU] It doesn't matter.
Just leave it alone.
[CHUTA] I actually think
it looks nice on her.
Why yes, he looked
just like that.
[MISUZU] Inspector Chips,
I'm sorry that I'm so late.
Just finishing up a composite
sketch of this groper, chu.
Something like this, chu?
Wait, that face... I think
I saw it in another division.
[CHIPS]
Chu?
That's the bag snatcher.
They look alike.
He tried to kidnap a baby.
Looks the same.
Bag snatching, a
baby-napping, and groping?
And the composite sketches were
the same for all three cases.
Does that mean it
was all the same guy?
[VIRGIL
Hm...
I'll run a search for this face
among the composite
sketches in our database.
What the--? It can't be!
[CHUTA, VIRGIL]
Huh?
[VERONICA]
What the heck is going on?
[NINOTCHKA]
I conducted a search for anyone
matching that facial data
within Shizuoka Prefecture
where the incidents occurred,
and I got 152 hits.
How are there so many?
Oh, that's simple, chu!
Because when alien
species like the Dunians,
who don't have transformation
abilities, come to Earth,
they're required to get
temporary cosmetic surgery
that makes them look
like Earthlings while visiting.
Yeah, but that doesn't mean
that they all have to have
the same face, does it?
Well, the Dunian government
is pretty lax, so, y'know...
I'll send 'em a stern
warning about that.
But this is really bad, chu.
If the culprit is one
of those look-alikes,
it's gonna be difficult
to find them, chu.
So what else do we know
about his appearance?
Yeah, in all three cases,
the suspect was wearing
a red hoodie and jeans.
Was there an SPH signal
detected at the crime scenes?
[NINOTCHKA] Well, unfortunately,
just like Earthlings,
they don't emit any SPH,
so we have no choice but to
interrogate all 152 of them.
Yeah, um, I was hoping to make
it home for dinner tonight.
Do you think we'll
be done by then?
Not a chance.
But isn't bringing peace to the
galaxy worth the price, chu?
Yeah, that's the spirit!
I'll let you guys
handle the interviews.
This case involves
three divisions
of the Investigations
Department, chu.
We have to work together, chu!
Well, Misuzu from Division Two
was the first to realize
that they were connected,
so I'd really hate
to steal her thunder.
[DOLUGH]
Wow, Chuta,
it sounds like nobody
wants to do this assignment.
[chuckles nervously]
[VERONICA] Well, we're
counting on you, Misuzu.
We can't do this
by ourselves, chu!
Heads up,
Investigations Department.
An arson case was
reported on Earth
and it's possible it's an
intergalactic incident.
Need someone there right away.
Yes! Finally an
exciting assignment!
This kinda thing is
right up my alley!
How can we possibly lose, chu?
Let's do it!
[ALL]
We got this!
Let's see now,
who should I send?
If it's an arson case, it'd be
best to let Division Two go.
Why?
Oh, yeah? And why is that?
Veronica from Division Five
hasn't fully recovered
from her surgery after the
remote control SPH case.
And I only recently
reattached Virgil
from Division One's
neck and legs.
Oh, come on, this is nothing.
Well, I guess I do
owe you my life, Doc.
We're all counting
on you, Division Two.
[ALL]
Yoyosa!
Actually, I'm pretty sure
Veronica and Virgil's wounds
have completely healed.
Of course they have.
I'm the one who
treated them, after all.
Then why say that?
I have a feeling that the
reason for Kokonose's smell
is about to become
abundantly clear.
[ALL groaning]
[MISUZU]
Let's go.
I suspect that smoke is
coming from the arson site.
[CHUTA]
The police are here.
[CHIPS]
A lot of intergalactic crimes
are recognized by Earthlings
as something that might
happen in their own society,
or that they're familiar with.
Actually, they're reported
to the police pretty often.
You'd be surprised, chu.
Let's get out of here.
[CHUTA]
Huh?
Hey, where are we going?
If we try to scope out
the crime scene now,
we won't be able to get close
because of all the police.
So we're gonna make
a detour, chu!
[ROBOTIC VOICE A] Identification
complete. You may now enter.
[CHUTA]
Whoa. What is this place?
[CHIPS]
It's an exclusive café!
You need either an
intergalactic passport
or an elDLIVE badge
just to get in.
It's a special place
where aliens can be
in their natural form.
Who knew this
kinda place existed?
Let's ask some questions.
Start over there, chu.
Now then.
We're looking for an arsonist.
Your help would be
greatly appreciated.
No thanks, honey.
Not interested.
Just tell me whatever you know
and this'll all be over quickly.
Wow, you're extremely annoying.
Sir, if you refuse to
cooperate with us,
I'll have to arrest you for
aiding and abetting a criminal.
[yelps]
[CHIPS]
Hold it, Misuzu!
That's going a little overboard,
don't you think, chu?
[CHUTA laughing]
Oh, now, darling,
don't be silly.
Of course you can't make
an omelet without milk.
Right, that's what
makes 'em so fluffy.
[COW ALIEN A] So what was it
you were investigating, moo?
[CHUTA] Well, ma'am,
it's an arson case.
[COW ALIEN A] Oh, you mean
that fire that happened
just around the
corner from here.
You'd better hurry up
and answer, or else I'll--
Misuzu, calm down, chu!
[CHUTA]
Uh, Sonokata.
[MELPLEIAN A]
Hey, you there!
Just what are you doing...
with my beloved?
Melpleian robot!
Oh, no, chu! That's an
actual Melpleian, chu!
[MELPLEIAN A]
Skaa.
Prepare to be---
[CHUTA]
Oh, wow! Look at that pouch!
Did you make that yourself?
The cross-stitching's
so beautifully detailed.
Thank you for noticing.
Yeah, of course!
And my sweetie-pie made
me this spiffy outfit, too!
[CHUTA]
Whoa, you can also make clothes?
[OCTOPUS ALIEN A]
My sweetie-pie is the best...
We can probably get some
information from them now, chu.
An arson case?
[CHIPS] We're trying to
find the suspect, chu.
Ah.
Y'know, come to think of it,
I saw a suspicious guy in a red
hoodie that was near the scene.
A red hoodie?
[CHIPS]
Could it have been this man?
Oh yeah, that's
definitely the guy.
[CHIPS, CHUTA gasp]
What the heck is going on, chu?
Certainly wasn't expecting
the arson to be caused
by the Dunian in the
red hoodie, too.
Purse snatching,
attempted kidnapping,
elbow groping, and now arson.
This guy had the same face
and was wearing the same thing
for every incident,
that must mean--
In the Bureau's database search,
there were 152
Dunians who showed up.
Just because they have
the same face and clothes
doesn't necessarily mean
they're the same person, chu.
Anyway, let's check out
the crime scene.
It's possible the suspect could
still be in the vicinity.
[grunts]
[MAN] Hey there, kids.
You got a minute?
Just got a few questions for ya.
You happen to see anyone
suspicious around here?
Only you.
[laughs]
You got me there, young lady!
I'm a detective
with the Shizuoka
prefectural police department.
Ya see, there was a
really nasty fire nearby.
Seems like it could be arson,
so we're looking for a suspect.
Well, we don't know anything!
Yes, we were just
passing through.
Ah, I see. Well,
that's good, then. Heh.
'Cause they say that criminals
always return to the
scene of the crime.
So you kids have some
business here or something?
Those are Shirobori Middle
School uniforms, right?
That's a long way away
from here, ain't it?
Uh, well...
[DOLUGH]
He suspects you, Chuta.
[CHUTA]
We're, uh--
We're on a date.
Well, well, aren't
you a lucky guy?
So where are you two
lovebirds going on said date?
[MISUZU]
At the movie theater nearby.
Fujiyama Cinema.
They're showing a revival of
Adults Just Don't Understand .
Right, Chutiekins?
[screams]
[HIDARU]
A movie revival, eh?
[MISUZU] That's right. My
Chutiekins just loves that one.
[HIDARU]
I see. Well, hold on a sec...
[CHUTA] Her-Her chest.
S-S-Sonokata's chest, it's--!
[MISUZU]
Yes, of course.
[DOLUGH] Calm down!
Your heart is beating too fast!
[CHUTA breathing heavily]
How 'bout that? It's
definitely playing there.
[COP A]
Hey, Detective!
I think we found someone
who looks suspicious.
Well, sorry to bother you kids.
Now have a good time, but don't
stay out too late, all right?
[MISUZU]
We won't.
[MISUZU sighs]
[CHIPS]
That was a close one, chu.
Thanks for the quick
movie information.
No problem at all, chu. Hmm...
Is something wrong?
Misuzu, turn around slowly, chu.
It's that face.
[CHIPS] He's wearing a red
hoodie and jeans, too, chu.
Let's box him in, and I'll
come at him from behind.
[CHUTA]
Uh-huh...
C'mon, get ahold
of yourself, Chuta!
[CHUTA] But I can... still
feel her chest on my arm.
You have to lower
your heart rate!
If you don't, you're gonna die!
[CHUTA]
They were so soft.
[DOLUGH] Don't you have
a mission to carry out?
[CHUTA]
Oh, yeah, right.
Hey, look, there's the
suspect right over there.
[CHUTA]
Crap!
This is Kokonose.
The suspect's getting away.
[CHIPS]
What happened, chu?
[CHUTA]
I was kinda out of it.
I'm so sorry!
This was my mistake!
[gasps]
I can't let him escape
because of me.
Dolugh, we need wings!
[DOLUGH]
Sympathy!
Hey, Dolugh, speed up!
[DOLUGH]
Sympathy!
We've almost got 'em!
[gasps]
Uh, hey, are you--? I-I didn't--
[CHIPS]
What's going on here, chu?
You move, I'll cut you.
Whoa, SPH.
We're officers of the
Space Police elDLIVE!
You're coming back to
the Bureau with us.
We have a lot of
questions for you.
[WOODY]
I was hoping... you'd say that!
[crying]
Oh, there's so much
that I wanna tell you!
I'm a little confused, chu!
[CHUTA] So your intergalactic
passport was stolen?
Yeah, that's right.
And without it,
I had absolutely nothing to
prove that I really am a Dunian,
which meant that I had no
way to report to elDLIVE.
So out of desperation,
you panicked and
tried bag snatching,
kidnapping, groping, and arson,
hoping that you'd get
captured by elDLIVE?
Well, mostly. I just want
you to catch the thief!
The guy who took it was
some weird Earthling
who was at this mixer with me.
[CHUTA]
Earthling?
[NINOTCHKA] Care to tell us what
this is all about, Mr. Marukobi?
Aw, man.
I guess the jig is up.
And just when things
were starting to get
interesting, too.
'Kay, let's start with why you
decided to steal the passport.
Well, it all began when I was
mistaken for somebody else,
and then got taken to a mixer.
I soon found out that everyone
there besides me was an alien,
and needless to say,
I was pretty surprised.
So I borrowed one
of their passports
and then researched a
bunch of cool stuff.
After that, I felt like
a badass hero
in a sci-fi movie or something!
I always knew there had
to be some good reason
I was born with this face!
And finally, it paid
off! Oh, yeah!
Discovering there are aliens
disguised as humans is huge!
And then I found out
that Space Police exist,
and that's even huger!
[CHIPS]
Well, that case is closed, chu.
Uh, thanks, Sonokata,
for earlier.
I mean, we almost lost
the suspect back there
'cause I dropped the ball.
So thanks a lot.
Uh. It was nothing.
[CHUTA]
Hm? I wonder what's wrong.
Normally, she'd be saying
something really mean to me
right about now.
[MISUZU]
Psychogenic?
Yes, that's right.
I think perhaps you panicked
a little when you saw Chuta
beginning to show
signs of maturing.
He managed to solve a case
without you around to help,
so you felt some
anxiety about the fact
that Chuta no longer needed you,
and your sense of dread
affected your sense of smell.
What? But that's insane.
Is there any evidence
to back all this up?
[LOVE]
Yes.
[MISUZU yelps]
You pervert!
[LOVE]
Oh, right, sorry.
As it turns out,
as soon as Officer Kokonose
slipped up today,
the SPH curtain stopped working.
[gasps]
That's right.
You were able to tolerate
his scent all on your own,
without help from
the SPH curtain.
My theory is that
your anxiety subsided
as soon as he was
found to be an error,
which then caused
your sense of smell
to return back to
normal after that.
No way.
[LOVE]
It's the undeniable truth.
Which means that this was
all my fault the whole time.
Worse, somewhere deep
down in my heart,
I was rooting for Officer
Kokonose to fail.
I'm...
I'm just the worst!
[crying]
[LOVE]
You've got the wrong idea.
You weren't actually hoping that
your partner would do poorly.
What caused your anxiety
was a frustration with yourself.
As you sat there watching
Chuta mature by your side,
your urge to mature
yourself just intensified.
It's a completely
natural response.
Besides, Chuta can
be so mysterious,
what with his ability to somehow
lift up those around him.
[LOVE]
That's right.
And I can give you proof
that you don't actually
want Officer Kokonose to fail.
I imagine you're still
getting just a hint
of that bad odor
from him, right?
I thought the device
couldn't completely mask it.
If that were caused by
someone else's failure,
there'd be nothing you could do.
This is a scent that only
your own growth can change.
It may entirely
disappear someday,
or perhaps instead it will
become as comforting to you
as the smell of that
grassy field back home.
Hey, Misuzu.
I just received a
report from Chips
about the arson investigation.
Nice job.
Thanks, Chief Laine.
Well, just keep
up the good work.
Yoyosa!
[LAINE]
Oh, by the way.
That new hairpin,
I think it really suits you.
Nice statement.
I question your sense
of style, Chief.
Ah, and there it is.
There's some of that
trademark Misuzu attitude!
[laughing]
[MISUZU] So Officer Kokonose's
foul stench was all in my head.
[LAINE]
I'm counting on you.
Yoyosa!
[door opens]
[LAINE]
Oh?
Ah, you're here.
[TONTO]
Chief Laine!
The Red Bean Paste Mochi
Galaxy lies ahead of us!
[LAINE]
What? This is an emergency!
We have to eat it all
before it goes bad! Oh, man!
[DOLUGH] Next time on
elDLIVE : "Your Voice..."
[LAINE]
It was only a dream.