[MAN A] You got a plan
to move the goods?
[MAN B] Piece-a-cake.
What about yours?
[MAN A]
Here, I'll show it to ya.
[MAN B]
Uh! You bastard.
[MAN A]
Damn right.
[KIESHI] I'm sure you already
know why you're here.
It's about Drago Bureau.
They boarded a smuggling ship
headed toward your solar system
and found a body
and this symbol.
I've seen that mark before!
[ISAAC]
That's everything.
Doctor Isaac, I have a question.
So far I've got
handcuffs, this badge,
and I assume a snazzy
uniform's coming,
but shouldn't I
also get a weapon?
[ISAAC]
Hm?
What kinda weapon
you have in mind?
A gun or a whistle or something.
Giving you either of
those would be a waste.
[CHUTA]
Huh?
Space criminals possess
abilities far beyond
what normal Earth science
is able to comprehend.
In order to beat them requires
a special kind of power.
The reason you were
chosen to join elDLIVE
is because you showed an ability
to harness just such a power
during your qualifying exam.
Guess we did.
I was quite surprised myself.
It was a remarkable performance.
Yeah, I guess so.
I feel you getting confident,
Chuta, and I like it.
Whoa, dude, that
sounds so creepy!
So, Doc, what's the secret to
making this special power work?
[ISAAC]
Body odor.
'Course, the clinical
term we use is SPH.
It's short for
"space pheromones."
So Dolugh's attack's
based on his odor?
[ISAAC]
Earthling's can't smell it,
but SPH can be used for
all kinds of attacks.
Whoa, that means when we had
that escapee the other day,
Sonokata defeated him
by using her body odor?
Please refrain from
being a pervert at work.
Oh, good! Misuzu
I take it that my kit's
all ready, Doctor?
Yes, yours is in the upper right
shelf with the red capsules.
Thanks.
What's wrong?
Sonokata, are you sick?
[MISUZU]
No.
The pills help me adapt to
the ship's environment.
[CHUTA gasping]
[DOLUGH] Seeing panties makes
Chuta's heart beat fast!
Hey! Don't say that!
I didn't see panties!
[gasps]
[MISUZU growls]
[MISUZU]
Pervert!
Hey! Over here, you guys!
[DOLUGH]
Chuta, you've been getting
so much more assertive, lately.
[DOLUGH] All the people
complimenting you
has done wonders
for your confidence.
Wow. You think so?
[TATEYAN]
Chuta, head's up!
Wha--?
[CHUTA]
Crap!
[DOLUGH]
Sympathy!
[whistle blows]
[CHUTA]
Dolugh! What if they saw you?
[STUDENT A]
Nice goal, Chuta!
[STUDENT B] Yeah, dude!
You got a cannon for a leg!
[STUDENT C]
Awesome!
Uh, thanks, guys.
[DOLUGH]
Chuta, you're so happy!
Heck yeah, I'm happy!
That goal was super cool!
[DOLUGH]
Yeah, and now you're talking
to more and more kids at school.
Yep!
People wanna be your friend when
you've got mad soccer skills!
Help! Thief! Someone,
catch that shoplifter!
[CHUTA]
Freeze, creep!
Dolugh! This guy should
be easy to sew up!
Sew him up!
[DOLUGH]
He shattered?
[screams]
[gasps]
[CHUTA]
Aunt Mimi! Are you okay?
Mimi, wake up! Wake up!
[DOLUGH] Shouldn't you be
looking after Aunt Mimi, Chuta?
[CHUTA] Once again someone got
hurt, and it's all my fault.
It's best if I don't
do anything at all.
Chuta.
[CHUTA gasps]
Dolugh, you're fading.
If you start thinking
bad things about yourself,
you'll be denying my existence,
and my body'll fade away.
[footsteps]
[MISUZU] You are not supposed
to use your SPH powers
in every day life.
It's against elDLIVE regulation.
Sonokata.
You see, that power
is not of the Earth.
It's too dangerous
to use haphazardly.
[CHUTA]
All right, I get it.
No, you don't. You only
understand a fraction of it.
[CHUTA]
Huh?
I took the liberty of cleaning
up your mess this time,
but if you do it again, the
punishment will be severe.
[DOLUGH]
Chuta, I can't help but notice
this is the meal you always
cook when you're depressed.
[CHUTA] I think...
I should quit elDLIVE.
[DOLUGH]
Don't be rash!
Chuta, becoming a space
policeman is the best thing
that's ever happened
to your confidence!
My confidence?
Mimi's hurt because
of my confidence!
Stupid! I shouldn't
have gotten involved!
[CHUTA] And after I swore I
wouldn't hurt anyone ever again,
I still managed to do it!
[DOLUGH]
Chuta! Red Alert!
I think you made too
much depression food!
[NURSE A]
Aw, how sweet of you.
You know It's still
visiting hours, though.
You can bring them to
her yourself if you want.
[CHUTA] Yeah, no, I think it'd
be better if you took it in.
Well, hey, you.
[CHUTA gasps]
Chuta, you finally came!
I still can't believe
one of the wall beams
was so old it fell down.
[CHUTA]
What?
That's weird. Her
memory's been changed.
Well, it could've
been worse, though.
it coulda hit my head
and knocked me silly!
No, wait, Aunt Mimi.
The truth is... that I--
Oh, Chuta, honey, what's wrong?
[CHUTA]
It would've been better...
...if I was the one
who got hurt, not you.
[gasps]
[MIMI]
Don't you dare say that!
I just meant, it'd be better
because you have to work.
Chuta, if you got hurt,
I wouldn't be able to sleep,
let alone bake muffins!
Watching you grow up
and waiting for you to
walk through the door
after school every day,
that is my whole
motivation for living!
It's only when you're doing
okay that I'm doing okay.
I'm... sorry, Auntie.
[MIMI]
Look at me.
I made myself cry with
my own little speech.
[CHUTA]
Don't cry.
Well, on the bright side, you've
been so much happier lately.
And confident, too.
[CHUTA]
Huh?
[DOLUGH] Mimi sees the changes
in you, just like I do.
[CHUTA] Sometimes I forget how
much she cares for me.
I have to be a stronger person.
It's the only way I'll
be able to protect her.
And her muffin shop!
Hey, look! Chuta,
I'm becoming solid again!
[CHIPS]
I see you, chu!
[CHUTA]
Huh? Sonokata?
It's time for our shift.
[CHUTA, MISUZU, CHIPS]
Yoyosa!
Nice salute.
Section Chief
Madigan's still out.
So until he's back, you
answer to me. You got that?
[CHUTA, MISUZU]
Yes, Chief!
Now, having said that,
I don't really have a
mission for your team
that matches your skill levels.
How 'bout you just
go study for school?
[CHUTA]
Huh?
Looks like we got
free time, chu.
Too bad.
I bet working on that case
would've been so fun, chu.
Um. Wait, which case?
[MISUZU]
You haven't heard?
Apparently, the thief you
blasted by your Auntie's shop
was an alien.
[gasps]
Then what are we
standing around here for?
We gotta arrest that jerk!
[MISUZU] I see that news
energized you. What's going on?
Well, he's a shoplifter.
And my auntie,
she can't run her store with
that crook still at large.
[CHIPS]
I don't like this.
It's not good to make an
investigation personal, chu.
What? Okay, I get it.
[MISUZU] No, Chips.
He's right this time.
Hold on, what?
[MISUZU]
We're not receiving good cases
because Kokonose's
rank is so low.
If we solve this,
he'll level up.
If we don't, chances
are he'll die.
Either outcome works for me.
[CHUTA]
What? Argh!
Forget it! I'll work this alone!
[MISUZU]
'Kay, good luck.
Oh, yeah, I'll arrest him.
Easy since I have no
idea where to start!
Chuta!
How did elDLIVE find out
the thief was an alien
in the first place?
I dunno.
They probably scanned the area
and noticed some difference
between him and humans.
Uh.
His SPH! That's gotta be it!
[MELIES]
Click here, and then double...
Uh, excuse me, Mr. Melies, sir?
[gasping]
How dare you!
My true form must never
be seen by others!
Moon guy has arms and
they're super shredded!
I'll have you know the number
of people who've seen my arms
is only... 50 thousand!
That's actually quite
a lot of people.
Shut up, what do you want?
[CHUTA] Um, I'm trying to catch
a shoplifting alien on Earth,
and I was wondering if you
kept SPH records in here.
[MELIES] You're running
your own investigation?
That's some nerve!
That's right. You gonna
help me with this or not?
[MELIES] Hm, he has the
most of the leverage here
since he saw my arms.
Fine! Long as you don't gab
about my muslces, I'll help!
[CHUTA]
Muscles? What muscles?
[MELIES] Just like fingerprints
on you Earthlings,
the SPH signature on
aliens is always unique.
No two are alike!
[CHUTA]
Wow.
[MELIES] I'm searching
for any sign of SPH
recorded near your home at
the time of the shoplifting.
And then I'll cross-reference
that with our database.
[beep]
[MELIES]
We got a match! That's him!
Hey, uh, he's done a
lot more than shoplift.
[CHUTA]
Really? What'd you find?
[MELIES]
It's bad. Way bad.
[CHUTA]
Uh, Chief?
[LAINE]
Huh?
[CHUTA] The alien shop-lifter
from my street...
...did you also know
that he's a murderer?
It's not your case,
how do you know?
[CHUTA]
I kinda, just, uh...
Earlier I saw Officer Kokonose
go to the SPH Research
Office to see Melies.
You must have
something on Melies
in order to get him to help.
All right, enough.
I thought I told you
guys to just go study.
And like I said: We're already
investigating that case.
I know. But can you let me
be a part of it, as well?
[LAINE]
Why are you so hung up on this?
I guess it's just--
Well, I think I have
do it to protect my--
[DOLUGH]
Chuta!
You were warned not to bring
your personal life into the job!
Right. I know.
Um, well, Chief,
it's just that...
...I'm worried if we don't catch
this murderous
shoplifting alien,
then people on that street
won't be able to live
their lives in peace.
And if he rips off any more
of them, well that's...
...even more tragic than when
the rice for your curry
comes out too mushy!
[LAINE]
Uh.
[ALL]
Uh?
[HARRY]
That's the worst thing you know?
[ALL laughing]
All right, bring in the culpret.
You made your case, Chuta!
Wait, Chief, are you sure?
I thought this crook
was a special case
and you had plans to mark him?
That's our Chief for ya.
Always shootin' from the hip.
[LAINE]
The suspect: Gumshoe Alien Jim.
He's wanted on charges
of larceny and murder.
Judging from the murder scene,
he killed his partner in a
meeting they were having
about how to ship their
stolen goods off the planet.
So tell me, what did
the criminals take?
They stole bubblegum.
He steals bubblegum?
Gumshoe Alien Jim's bodily
form is similar to bubblegum.
For his race, it has certain
medicinal properties.
He killed someone... for gum.
Well, they don't have it
on the Gumshoe planet.
A short supply plus high demand
creates a lure of easy money
that pushes already
bad guys to murder.
Any leads on where he might be?
[LAINE]
Yes. One.
[CHIPS]
He drives a yellow truck, chu?
[LAINE] Right, intel
assumes he's driving it
to haul around his
stolen bubblegum.
[MELIES]
Hm.
The alien's SPH
signature is weak!
I can't find...
Huh. Looks like his
arms are gone again.
I also can't seem to locate
him on satellite either.
He's driving a big yellow truck.
Shouldn't we just be
looking for that?
Hey! I see something in
the truck's windshield!
[CHUTA]
The reflection.
Mount Fuji?
[ALL gasp]
[MELIES] By analyzing
the angle of the sun
casting Mount Fuji's reflection,
I can calculate the truck's
position on Earth.
Bingo! It's Tomei Highway!
[CHUTA grunts]
He always messes up, chu!
Do you see the truck?
It should be right here.
Hey, where you going?
It'd be best for our search
if you just stay here.
In fact, sit out the
investigation altogether.
What?
Bye.
Chuta! I smell bubblegum!
It's coming from
there! Smell it?
[CHUTA]
It's a truckstop. They sell gum.
Yes, but this scent is
Snap-Snap bubblegum!
They only sell that at candy
shops like the one on my street.
I think we found him!
This is elDLIVE!
Gumshoe Alien Jim, come
out with your hands up!
How has he managed to
hide a giant yellow truck?
[BOTH yelp]
Owie, that hurt.
Oh, good gravy.
[JIM] You may have found me,
but you won't bring me in!
[DOLUGH]
Chuta! It's the yellow truck!
[CHUTA] Which means our
suspect... is this puny alien!
Hey, you bumped into
me on the street!
It's because of you
blasting my body suit
I can't be big no more!
I'm gonna kill you
dead, elDLIVE!
[CHUTA laughs]
This guy must be the smallest
murderer in history!
I'm with the Space
Police elDLIVE!
You have the right
to remain silent.
You have the right to an-- Ah!
[JIM] Ha-ha! Warned you not
to mess with me, space pig!
Oh, that's it!
[CHUTA yells]
[JIM] Nice kick!
Your grandma teach you?
What is that thing?
[MISUZU]
That's SPH.
[CHUTA]
Sonokata.
Normal physical attacks have no
effect on a suspect using SPH.
[screams]
[CHUTA]
Her SPH.
That's one powerful body odor.
When you say it like
that, it's gross.
You're right. Quiet now.
Chuta! The suspect's gone!
Oh, no!
Little guy like him couldn't
have gotten far, chu!
[rustling]
Surprise, jerks!
You let your guard down!
--[CHUTA] Sonokata!
--[CHIPS] Misuzu!
Here's what ya get for
messing with Gumshoe Jim:
A smothered partner!
He's using his SPH to
stick to her super tight.
I can't get an attack in
without him hurting her, chu!
[DOLUGH] But, Chuta, if we don't
do anything, she'll suffocate!
[CHUTA]
But what can we do?
Sonokata, don't do it!
I can't believe bubblegum
can be so evil, chu!
[CHUTA]
I feel so useless!
Chuta!
Do you remember what
we did that time
Mimi got gum stuck on her
shirt and it wouldn't wash off?
Aww, look at this!
[DOLUGH] If we do now what we
did then, we'll save her.
You think it'll work?
As long as you imagine
it, I can do it!
'Kay! Here goes!
The key to removing gum
is to freeze it off!
[DOLUGH]
Sympathy!
Space Pheromone's
Freezing Gum-off!
Wha--? I'm so... cold!
--It worked!
--Yay, chu!
[MISUZU coughing]
[MISUZU]
I'm fine.
Close one.
[MISUZU] Thanks for saving me,
Officer Kokonose.
But that doesn't mean
I like working with you!
Hey! You could just
say thank you!
This time you're under
arrest for sure, chu!
[JIM]
But I'll die.
We prefer rehabilitation, chu.
[JIM]
No, no. I'm gonna die!
He's gonna blow, chu!
[MISUZU]
Get down!
I'm reading a huge SPH signal.
[DOLUGH]
That smells good.
[gasps]
[CHUTA]
She's... so close.
You saved me, now I saved you.
This way, you can never try
holding it over my head.
No way! I would never do that!
[CHIPS] Hey, you guys!
What's with the crater, chu?
That symbol!
[RIGGS]
I think we know what that means.
We do. They killed him
and left that symbol.
Just as a warning.
We're dealing with a
criminal organization
that commits heinous acts
throughout the galaxy.
DeMille.
Who? What?
[LAINE] Long ago, and
20,000 light years away,
DeMille destroyed a planet.
A planet just like Earth.
So now these guys are
headed right toward us?
[CHUTA] Hey, Aunt Mimi!
You excited to go home?
[TATEYAN]
Yo!
[CHUTA]
Tateyan. Why're you here?
The candy shop lady
told me what happened.
Your friend brought
rice crackers
as a get-well-soon gift!
Oh, nice. Thanks, Tateyan.
[TATEYAN]
Has anyone ever told you
that your aunt looks like
pop idol Yui Sakuraebi?
I've never heard that. Sorry.
That's okay.
I had a weird dream.
I don't remember all the
details, but I was about to die
until you came over
and saved me.
[CHUTA]
Dream, huh.
[DOLUGH] elDLIVE must've
changed his memories.
Well, you know, sometimes...
a dream is just a dream.
Good point. Just a dream.
You're a pretty
wise dude, Chuta.
[DOLUGH]
And you're gullible!
Even though it was a dream,
it's like, deep down I know
we're friends for real.
[DOLUGH] You know what
this feeling is, Chuta?
It's you starting to form
deep connections with others.
[CHUTA] You don't have to
comment on my every emotion!
[MIMI crying]
[CHUTA]
Aunt Mimi, why're you crying?
[wails]
My sweet little Chuta
finally made a friend!
I think you're
overreacting a bit!
[DOLUGH]
But she's not, Chuta.
Ever since the falling
incident as a kid,
and until you joined elDLIVE,
you've been completely
friend-less, Chuta.
[CHUTA]
Maybe you're right.
I didn't realize
how alone I was.
I forgot what it felt like
to even have friends.
In fact, over the last few days,
I've realized a whole
bunch of things.
About my family. My friends.
And about myself.
Dolugh's right.
The best thing that's
ever happened to me
is joining elDLIVE.
Ah. Looks like someone's
made it official.
Wow, The uniform
looks great on you!
I like it, Chuta.
You pull off this
look pretty well!
Whatever you do, do not
wear this outfit to school.
Of course I won't!
I'm not that dumb!
Next up: Chuta's
entrance ceremony!
[CREW]
Yoyosa!
[CREW MEMBER A]
High-speed nav-com online.
[CREW MEMBER B]
Your orders, Captain?
[CAPTAIN]
Commence.
[CREW MEMBER A]
Target is blue,
rocky planet in outer
arm of the Milky Way.
It's Shirobori Middle
School, to be exact!
Right, Captain?
That's right. And I can't
wait to see Chuta again.
[MAN C]
No doubt about it.
[MAN D]
Yup.
[GIRL B]
You're right.
[MISUZU] Officer Kokonose's
naming skills are...
[ALL]
...zero!
[DOLUGH]
Next time, on elDLIVE :
"A Pursuer From
the Past: Part 1."
[CHUTA]
Freezing Gum-off attack!
[MISUZU]
Oh, brother.