[CROWD cheering]
[MALE SUBJECT]
Look! King Fernando himself!
[FEMALE SUBJECT]
Your Majesty!
Please, you have to save
your strength, my dear.
I'm sure you'll be the
picture of health, Majesty.
Once that witch is
burned down to ashes.
Indeed.
I pray that the Lord not hearken
me home to His side quite yet.
What of my wife?
And my young Alfonso here?
[YOUNG ALFONSO gasps, yelps]
[ESMERALDA]
Uh?
[FERNANDO]
Take him in, Esmeralda.
What follows is no
easy thing to see.
[ESMERALDA]
Yes.
Come along, Alfonso.
[CROWD yelling]
[FEMALE SUBJECT B]
Look at her.
Pregnant with some imp,
no doubt!
[MALE SUBJECT B]
God above!
[MALE SUBJECT C]
Burning to death,
and she doesn't make a sound.
That proves she's
a witch, right?
[MALE SUBJECT D] All those
people that died of the plague,
those lives are on her head!
[MALE SUBJECT E]
Death to the witch!
[MALE SUBJECT F]
Burn for all eternity!
[FEMALE SUBJECT C] This is for
my daughter, you monster!
[BABY crying]
--[CROWD murmurs]
--[FEMALE SUBJECT D] What?
[BABY crying]
How can this be?
Mendosa, do you hear that?
[clattering]
[gasping]
[MAKAI KNIGHT growls]
[MENDOZA]
Protect the king!
[groans]
[CROWD screaming]
The man in that
resplendent armor
was an ally of the witch?
A knight in thrall to
the princes of Hell. He'd been
rotting away in our dungeon
until he made his escape.
Why are you standing there?
Give chase, you simpletons!
Every man who can ride,
on a horse!
[FERNANDO sighs]
He won't get far with
a babe in arms, Mendoza.
Take heart.
Would that you are right,
your Majesty.
--[FERNANDO coughing]
--[OCTAVIA gasps]
I fear the strain this
has placed upon you.
We must get you safely abed now.
What are you waiting for?
[OCTAVIA]
Yes.
[FERNANDO groans]
[MENDOZA]
You have burned,
but the whelp within you
did not share in your fate.
There will come the day
when your kind are nothing
but a memory. I will send
your foul confederacy
to the pit of the damned.
[GERMÁN]
The witch hunts of Valiante.
While being burned at the stake
for cursing King Fernando,
the witch Anna gave
birth to a child.
It was taken by the demon
that came to feast
upon the burning witch's soul.
Try though they might
to overtake the rider,
the King's army
pursued him in vain.
It was as though
demon and child alike
had simply vanished
from the world of man.
[GERMÁN] Once health had
returned to the King,
he called for a witch hunt
throughout his domain,
at Mendoza's urging.
For the crime of trying
to assassinate Mendoza,
the warlock Guillermo
was the first to fall.
[GUILLERMO groans]
[GUILLERMO screaming]
[GERMÁN]
He was by no means the last.
[SOLDIER A]
Don't let him escape!
[SOLDIER B]
There, in the alley!
[SOLDIER C]
After him!
[WARLOCK A grunts]
[WARLOCK B grunting]
[WARLOCK B groans]
[SOLDIERS gasp]
[SOLDIER F grunts]
[SOLDIERS groaning]
Ah!
[groans]
[WARLOCKS whimper]
[inaudible]
[GERMÁN]
In a single year,
over a hundred witches and
warlocks were killed.
When it came,
death was a blessing.
[MEN laughing]
[GERMÁN]
The King's people
were twisted by such
cruelty all around them.
Tongues whispered
damning suspicions,
fingers pointed in the dark.
Under the auspices of
the ongoing hunt,
Valiante sent armies
to surrounding lands,
consolidating its power.
Even I know of
that part, handsome.
This place was a holdout.
Valiante didn't conquer it
until about a year ago.
[GERMÁN]
Right.
Which brings this 17-year-old
tale to an end.
How's that for
pillow-talk, precious?
[PROSTITUTE] Terrible.
What a pitiful ending.
You still haven't told me what
happened to the demon knight,
or the witch's baby
he ran off with.
[chuckles] Wouldn't
Mendoza like to know.
He's hunted them
to this very day.
Awful man.
You promised me a story that
would pique my interest.
What a waste of time.
[GERMÁN] 'Course it was.
That was the official version.
What if the truth
was far afield?
Go on. [gasps]
[GERMÁN] What would happen,
if you looked at the same tale
through the eyes of
the condemned witch?
[PROSTITUTE]
Oh, devil take the witch!
Who cares what she thought?
She bartered away her soul
to Hell in trade for magic,
just like they all do.
It's disgusting.
Well, say whatever you like,
but this next part of the story
may leave you feelin' otherwise.
How'd you like me to tell you
the God's honest truth
about witches? Far from
being in league with demons,
it's a witch's job
to seal 'em away.
Seal away?
How so?
Shouldn't that be
handled by a priest?
Priests can't do
anything about 'em,
'cept piss themselves
before they get torn apart.
[laughs]
I think our local cleric
would take issue
with that statement.
Oh, he can squawk
all he wants.
Fact is a fact.
Hm. I'm still not
convinced, handsome.
Didn't the King get better
after they executed that witch
who was said to have cursed him?
That means the hex died with
the woman who placed it.
[meows]
[GERMÁN] Maybe.
Maybe it was just a coincidence,
or maybe the witch was framed.
[PROSTITUTE]
By who?
A demon.
Or a human who's in league
with 'em, at the very least.
[laughs] Impossible.
If they were real,
these demons of yours,
we'd be hearing about attacks
damn near every day.
You know, this work's had me
warming beds in capitols
and backwaters alike,
and I've never laid eyes
on a single one
of these demons you speak of.
Oh?
Well I've got a demon
I can introduce you to.
[PROSTITUTE] Easy now!
The money comes first!
How mercenary of you. And here
I thought my roguish charm
had already sealed the deal.
I'm not a charity, handsome.
I'll level with ya.
I'm a little light on
coin right now. I--
Well, that's it, then.
Wait, don't go!
I'll find some!
[knocking]
[OLD MAN] Hey! Germán!
Your boy's here to get you!
He says to put on your pants
and drag your worthless
hide downstairs already!
Really? I didn't peg
you for the type.
Yeah! Too bad he didn't inherit
my lust for life, though.
Just tell him his dear father
is trying to do as the Lord
commanded us all: to
love thy neighbor as thyself!
[OLD MAN] He says you'd
better not show your face again!
He's worse than
a wife, that one.
Damn it! Ah!
Wait! Beloved fruit
of my loins!
I seem to have forgotten a
certain something! You know...
Can you do your
old man a kindness?
[LEÓN grutns]
[GERMÁN groans]
That was a rock!
What a looker.
About sixteen, I'd guess?
[GERMÁN] He's seventeen.
God love him!
Same age as that baby
from your story.
If the kid were
still alive, that is.
[GERMÁN inhales]
Yeah, you're right.
But that's a pretty big "if."
[PROSTITUTE grunts]
You cad!
[gasps]
[chuckles]
[MENDOZA] Ah, so my
quarry finally surfaces.
I've received word of
a father and child
near the outskirts of Leiden
whose deeds are passing strange.
Leiden. So they fled
the kingdom after all.
[MENDOZA sighs] It's no wonder
we couldn't find them.
This child that
you speak of,
did they mention whether
it's a boy or not?
If it is,
he could ruin everything
we've been working so hard for.
[MENDOZA] Set your mind
at ease, Octavia.
I have already taken action.
[PROSTITUTE]
Hey.
I've been thinking about
what you told me before.
Have you ever seen a demon?
That I have.
[PROSTITUTE]
Liar.
Not about that.
Thing is,
they don't look the way priests
always make them out to.
In fact, a lot of the time,
they're closer to animals.
They devour the unwitting
from the inside out.
After that, they assume
the prey's identity.
No one's the wiser,
till the demon
gets hungry again.
That's horrible.
All right, let me ask
you something.
I've been hearin' rumors
about this place,
and brothel customers who never
make it back to their homes.
That kind of thing
happens a lot.
Men get bored of their wives
after a bite of
the forbidden fruit.
[GERMÁN] Huh. Wish it were
that simple, but it's not.
There's a Horror skulking
about, bet my life on it.
[PROSTITUTE]
A Horror?
[GERMÁN] That's what
demons were called,
at least before
the Church anyway.
[PROSTITUTE]
Tell me something,
how do you know for certain that
there's a Horror around here?
[GERMÁN sniffs]
It's the smell.
[PROSTITUTE laughs]
You're awful!
Well, looks like the demon
down here is hungry.
I say we give it what it wants.
You would do that?
Even though I have no money?
[PROSTITUTE] Make sure
you leave me satisfied.
[PROSTITUTE gasps, moans]
[GERMÁN gasps]
[HORROR screams]
Ha!
[GERMÁN grunts]
[HORROR groans]
[PROSTITUTE screams]
[HORROR gags]
[GERMÁN] See?
What did I tell you?
Horrors afoot.
[HORROR] That knight
who got away was you.
Listen well, demon,
you deserve to know the name
of the man who bested you.
Germán Luís.
Your kind know me as
the Makai Knight, Zoro!
[crying]
[GERMÁN]
And the child is...
[gasps]
[HORROR SOLDIER grunts]
[LEÓN]
Took you long enough.
That witch's brat, are you him?
Yes or no?
I'm León Luís.
It is in my blood
to purge this world
of Horrors like you.
[LEÓN yells]
[GERMÁN]
...the golden knight, Garo!
[HORROR A] It was him,
the boy on the street.
[GERMÁN] Don't tell me that
you're finished already.
I thought it would take a lot
more poking than that.
[LEÓN, HORROR SOLDIER grunting]
[LEÓN grunts]
[HORROR SOLDIER groans]
[HORROR SOLDIER groaning]
[LEÓN panting]
[HORROR SOLDIER groans]
[SOLDIERS scream]
[HORROR SOLDIER groaning]
[LEÓN growls]
[LEÓN yells]
[LEÓN grunts]
[HORROR SOLDIER screams]
[HORROR SOLDIER bellowing]
[LEÓN grunts]
[HORROR SOLDIER screaming]
[crying]
[GERMÁN]
Look, León,
that is where your mother
met a fiery end
so that you might live.
Remember it!
Mother.
You let me return to the shack,
alone, because you knew
they'd come looking
for me there! Some father.
Think of it as
part of your training.
If you can't even handle
the likes of those fools,
then what's the point?
Are we really going
now, to Valiante?
We are, back to the land
where we lost her.
[horse whinnies]
[FERNANDO] Let us celebrate
the birthday of my precious son,
and heir to my throne.
To Prince Alfonso!
--[CROWD cheering]
--[SUBJECT G] Congratulations!
[MALE SUBJECT H]
It's the Prince!
[FEMALE SUBJECT E]
Prince Alfonso!
[FERNANDO]
May the hero of our realm,
the Knight of Light,
smile upon you.
[ALFONSO]
You honor me greatly, Father.
Mother, too. [chuckles]
Only yesterday,
you but came to my knee.
Throughout your childhood,
you were so frail.
It does my heart good
to see how you've grown.
I love you more
than I can ever say.
[CROWD murmurs]
As do I.
For twenty years,
you have kept me safe from harm.
Now it is time for me
to show our land
the same kind of
devotion and care.
--I thank you, dear Mother.
--[CROWD cheering]
[ESMERALDA]
Alfonso.
I have worn this pendant
for protection
since I was a babe in arms.
Take it, it's yours now.
[CROWD murmurs]
[applause]
[OCTAVIA gasps]
[OCTAVIA]
That symbol.
[MENDOZA]
The time draws near.
Once our preparations
are finished,
there's not a force under
Heaven that can stop us.
[GARM]
Tell me, O Golden Knight,
of the pattern that
covers half your flesh.
Will it serve as the flame
that destroys evil?