[LEÓN]
Damn you...
Why?!
[GERMÁN grunts]
[LEÓN gasps]
[MENDOZA]
Ages ago,
our forebears the Knights
and Alchemists who founded
the once thriving network
of Watchdog Centers,
sealed a certain demon
within this cave.
[GERMÁN gasps]
My God.
[MENDOZA] The great demon,
Anima, will be resurrected.
It will waken and engorge
itself on the Horrors
pouring through the Makai Gates.
And when its power is
bridled to my will...
the secret of immortality
will be mine.
[LEÓN]
Old man.
[JIRUBA] Quickly now.
Germán is waiting for you.
[ALFONSO] León, are you
certain you're all right?
Yes. Try not to worry.
Come on.
[JIRUBA] You must hurry.
Germán is waiting.
[LEÓN]
After all that? Really?
[JIRUBA]
His actions were a ruse.
Mendoza must work without
obstruction. Anima must awaken.
He intends to let the beast
rise to fight it head on.
Earning Mendoza's trust was
a tactic all along.
He's a sly old fox, you have
to give him that much.
[JIRUBA] "I shall clear the way
for all of you. Please, hurry."
That is your father's message.
Hear, and heed well.
Now, I retire to silence.
The toil of words
I leave behind.
Reckless old scoundrel.
Exactly the sort of
thing he'd pull.
[EMA] The moon is on
the wane, gentlemen.
There's a certain thrill in this
if one has the heart for it.
Ah. Never mind. Just try not
the spoil the mood by dying.
But of course. Now
courage, friends.
For the good of Valiante!
Indeed.
This time without fail.
[GHOSTLY VOICES scream]
[screaming continues]
Are they... Makai?!
They're knights,
and alchemists!
[MENDOZA] Quite a few.
Drawing out Anima's power
requires proportional sacrifice.
Monstrous, even for you.
In ancient times, normal
humans would suffice.
As a summoning medium
they were easily accessible.
The Council believes I harvest
my offerings from the general
population, but, as in much
else, they are wrong.
The witch hunts were not
chiefly an effort to chip away
at your brothers and
sisters, my friend.
For this ritual, I needed
souls of a special caliber.
Come, Knight. You must
admit, t'was quite clever.
And we were convinced you'd
burned those men and women
to quell the fires
of your own hatred.
Oh, I take great satisfaction
searing the Council
with its own idiocy.
Ha! If you have the chance.
Garm, whatever else may be
said of her, is not dense.
She's far too sly to engage in
a battle she knows is lost.
At the end of the day, the
Watchdog Center's Oracle
is prepared to destroy
this whole land.
You may wager she did
not come to that lightly.
She is a formidable tactician.
As oracles go, her decisions
display a modicum of what
might be called good sense.
Yet, for all the warp and
weft of her stratagems,
many details slip past.
Yes, All just as well,
honestly speaking.
As I intend to foil her
plan, and cut you down.
That is my hope, at any rate.
[MENDOZA chuckles]
[OCTAVIA seethes]
[MENDOZA] Your superiors wish
for Anima's resurrection.
What a quandary!
Does the gallant Zoro become the
dog that turns on its master?
Well, I'm not sworn to protect
their interests, am I?
Nor yours either. I'm in the
business of protecting lives.
[MENDOZA] Mm. You disappoint me,
Germán Luís. I expected better.
I've not fallen far enough
for you to expect
anything of me save enmity.
[HORRORS growl]
[MENDOZA]
Your idealism is pathetic.
Bound by your duty to protect.
But naïveté is a darkness.
The scales drawn o'er our eyes.
You Makai Knights are
a study in that truth.
[OCTAVIA yells]
[OCTAVIA groans]
[GERMÁN grunts]
I'm sorry. You were saying?
There was something in there
about naïveté. Please, go on!
[GERMÁN grunts]
[GERMÁN growls]
[HORRORS growl]
[GERMÁN grunts]
--[GERMÁN grunts]
--[HORRORS growl]
[OCTAVIA gasps]
[GERMÁN yells]
[MENDOZA groans]
[OCTAVIA]
You bastard!
--[OCTAVIA screams]
--[GERMÁN grunting]
[GERMÁN]
Damn it.
[OCTAVIA groaning]
[GERMÁN grunts]
[GERMÁN gasps, groans]
[MENDOZA chuckles]
You paused when you had
the chance to kill me.
Yes. Ladies are my weakness,
but don't let your
guard down just yet.
[GERMÁN grunts]
This'll do for now, I
suppose! Much obliged!
So that was your plan, eh?
[MENDOZA]
I think not!
[GERMÁN whistles]
[MENDOZA growls]
[MENDOZA gasps]
[MENDOZA grunts]
[OCTAVIA]
Master Mendoza.
He'll return with the other
meddlesome fools shortly.
[MENDOZA]
Let it begin.
[EMA]
Seal after intolerable seal!
Has he nothing better to do?
[EMA sighs]
[ALFONSO] Uncle waits for
us beyond this point.
[LEÓN]
There's no time to waste.
[footsteps]
[LEÓN]
What is this?
Oh, damn it all! How many?
Gentlemen, hold on.
[ALFONSO, EMA, LEÓN gasp]
[ALFONSO, EMA, LEÓN scream]
[LEÓN, EMA, ALFONSO gasp]
What the...? Where are we?
[EMA]
Wherever Mendoza sent us.
And we may assume its boundaries
will continue to grow.
Before long, the back
will be out of reach.
[ALFONSO]
What must we do?
You knights stand aside.
I'll handle this one.
Now, I counted three
transmitters total.
[GERMÁN gasps]
[GERMÁN groans]
Mendoza, you ol' bastard.
You knew from the beginning
where my true loyalties were.
Doesn't bode well,
I'd be a fool to think he's
not prepared for the others.
[GERMÁN] And so much for a
moment to collect my thoughts.
Quite the gathering, I see.
[GERMÁN] Very well.
Friendly warning, however.
You've cornered a wolf!
And he's not about to
let these gates close!
[rumbling]
[GERMÁN]
Wha...?!
[GERMÁN] Maybe I did
need the rest of him.
[HORRORS growl]
[GERMÁN grunts]
--[GERMÁN yells]
--[HORROR G roars]
[GERMÁN yells]
--[GERMÁN yells]
--[HORRORS roar]
[HORROR G roars]
[GERMÁN growls]
[GERMÁN] Heh. I'll just
leave this here for now.
Can't have you closing on us.
[GERMÁN gasping]
[HORRORS roar]
[GERMÁN grunts]
[GERMÁN]
All right. Time to sink or swim!
[GHOSTLY VOICES scream]
[MENDOZA]
What a glorious sound.
[MENDOZA] My bitterness softens
with each anguished scream.
Mendoza was clearly equipped
for our infiltration in advance.
I fear this augurs rather
poorly for uncle's charade.
That jackass couldn't even last
long enough for us to reach him.
The man put Mendoza off
his guard the best he could.
[gasps]
[EMA] Ha! Got 'em!
Right, here's the plan.
Destroy the objects at the
ends of these threads.
No time to lose!
--Easy enough.
--You may count on us!
[ALFONSO]
We haven't a moment to spare!
[LEÓN]
We're coming, old man.
Don't lose heart.
Hold on just a bit longer.
[GERMÁN panting]
[HORRORS growl]
--[HORRORS growl]
--[GERMÁN grunting]
[GERMÁN panting]
Oh, hell I can't maintain.
--[GERMÁN grunts]
--[HORRORS roar]
[GERMÁN sighs, grunts]
--[HORROR X roars]
--[GERMÁN grunts]
[HORRORS growl]
[GERMÁN] Easy, now.
Not just yet, handsome.
I'm still kicking!
Ha. I'd love to oblige you.
Regrettably, I've never been
the sort of fellow who's
had the good sense to die!
[EMA exhales]
[LEÓN, EMA, ALFONSO gasp]
[ALFONSO]
We're back!
[EMA groans]
--[LEÓN] Ema!
--[ALFONSO] Oh, no!
Don't patronize me.
Now, come on.
We haven't the luxury
to slow down.
[EMA gasps]
What?!
What is this?
Someone's notion of a joke that
isn't remotely humorous.
[ALFONSO] Impossible. This may
well take ages to break through.
Then we've no choice
but to use force.
Spoken like an imbecile!
Damn it, there's
no other option!
Do you know how
powerful this is?
Think strategically for once.
If you could break though,
you'd be in no shape
to fight afterwards!
My old man is waiting for me.
[EMA gasps]
If we don't do all we
can to get to him,
he'll piss and moan for days.
Well, we can't abide that.
Very well. We'll take
turns with the barrier.
All right.
Great. That's settled.
Now get to it!
[LEÓN]
Let's go!
[LEÓN yells]
[ALFONSO yells]
[GHOSTLY VOICES scream]
Someone approaches.
Master, allow me to annihilate
them on your behalf.
My child, you haven't the power.
But, sir! I beg you to
witness my devotion!
Please. Lend me the
power to smite them.
I will not disappoint!
I would see the world
your genius has conceived
at last come to pass.
Master Mendoza, I long for
the honor to contribute!
I care not the cost! I will
destroy the Makai Knights!
[MENDOZA] If you speak
true, take up the staff.
Let us see the substance
of your convictions.
[OCTAVIA]
Observe me, Master.
[OCTAVIA screams]
[GERMÁN pants]
Steady now.
León's almost here.
I can feel it.
[LEÓN screams]
--[GERMÁN grunts]
--[HORROR roars]
Not yet, dammit!
If I don't last long enough,
he'll piss and moan for days.
[LEÓN, ALFONSO yell]
[LEÓN yells]
[ALFONSO, LEÓN yelp, groan]
Old man, I'm here!
You took your time, huh?
Y'know, I had half a mind
not to wait for you.
--[LEÓN panting]
--[GERMÁN] Son...
Forgive me if I restrain my
praise till all this is over.
The way still needs clearing!
--[GERMÁN grunts]
--[HORRORS roar]
[GERMÁN groaning]
No! Old man, wait!
That's it for me.
This body's had enough.
[ALFONSO]
Uh...
[EMA gasps]
[gasps] Uncle.
That son of a bitch.
I underestimated your stupidity.
Any woman who'd choose to ruin
a face like yours is a fool.
I liked your freckles.
I'd be careful if I were you.
Just so happens
my son is up there.
León Luís. You may
have heard of him.
[GERMÁN]
It is in his blood
to protect this world
from those such as you.
Legend calls him the
Golden Knight, Garo!
[GERMÁN gasps]
[GERMÁN]
I know his strength.
God, do I know it. [groans]
For he is my son, and no
father has ever been prouder.
You may call me Germán Luís,
Makai Knight.
Also known by the name...
Zoro!
[HORRORS growl]
[GARM]
The chivalrous silhouette.
The gaze that looks ever past
the horizon into tomorrow.
The spirit that protects
at all costs.