[ANIMA roars]
That's great.
The monster has a force field?
[ANIMA roars]
[LEÓN]
Uh!
[ZARUBA]
The chance is slight,
but we have some capacity
to neutralize it.
[LEÓN] Yes, well, some is
more than enough for me!
[MENDOZA] How disappointing.
Seems not even this creature
is invincible. Death
is still its master.
Alas, no living thing
escapes the icy grip.
This flesh and blood are
forever moored to decay.
Fate is cruel. Wouldn't
you agree, Golden Knight?
I don't know about all that, but
you're about to know firsthand.
[MENDOZA] A-ha! I am not
subject to the same laws!
I shall drink of
immortality. Mark me!
Now, this moment,
I alone will transcend!
[MENDOZA gagging]
Uh!
[EMA groans]
[ALFONSO grunting]
[LEÓN panting]
[MENDOZA]
A curious sensation.
I imagined the power of God
as a searing white flame.
Rather, 'tis cold like a vein
of some implacable ore.
[EMA grunts, panting]
[ALFONSO groans]
[MENDOZA] However this gift
chooses to manifest itself.
Let us test its boundaries.
[LEÓN]
Mendoza!
[LEÓN yells]
[MENDOZA chuckles]
This power surpasses the wildest
boundaries of imagination!
Death is my master
no more. I am eternal.
Really? Live it up now,
freak of nature!
Damned if I'll let whatever you
are run loose in this world!
You wound me in vain.
Can you not see that
my destruction is simply
beyond the skill of any man?
Indeed, not even God
himself can stop me.
And you are an insect.
[LEÓN groaning]
You are not the end of me, boy.
No mere Makai Knight shall
have the pleasure of undoing
such unfathomable power.
Impossible.
[ALFONSO groaning]
On your feet! Rise like a man!
Once you've taken
up the sword,
you've made a solemn pact until
your last shuddering breath!
If there's a drop of
blood left in your veins,
how dare you give up?!
Master, I...
Now stand! Your fight
has only just begun!
Draw deep and recommence!
You must fulfill your
sworn duty Alfonso,
to protect this land
as a Makai Knight!
Master, thank you.
Duty ever comes first.
I'm coming, Keep fighting, León.
The Golden Knight is
to me but a child.
Thus wound I the Council
fools who spurned me.
You vile, pitiable saplings.
Grasping at the shadow of
immorality through procreation.
Blood is meaningless.
You inherit only death.
Should you succumb before
passing on your seed,
you leave a barren legacy.
[MENDOZA] The very idea is
contemptible! A fool's gamble.
Look upon me. This body's
the realization of what man
only dreams of!
[LEÓN]
You're wrong.
[MENDOZA]
Mm?
[LEÓN]
I understand now.
I know the nature of
what I've inherited.
[LEÓN yelps]
[LEÓN] Our forebears
passed down something.
Beyond themselves.
Beyond death.
[LEÓN groans]
They were merely animals
that reveled in carnality.
Foolish and desperate
to extend their blood.
They barely had a taste
of the immortal life.
Sewer rats are nobler. At
least they are not deceived.
[LEÓN] Our legacy is more
than just bloodlines.
It's our desire to protect!
[panting] We are not cowards.
We face death for the
sake of the future!
Naïve boy.
[EMA groaning]
[gasps]
Germán's blade!
[EMA]
Of course.
Now, let us have done
with this once and for all.
I'm not about to let you rest
on your laurels yet, friend.
Damn fool.
León!
[EMA]
Alfonso!
[EMA yells]
You're still alive! Uh!
[ALFONSO grunts]
Uncle... No...
[ALFONSO yells]
León!
[LEÓN] What we inherit
is larger than ourselves.
[LEÓN roars]
[LEÓN grunting]
[LEÓN] Someone like you could
never hope to understand.
Why should one such
as I even care
to comprehend a
vermin's feelings?
[LEÓN]
Well, Old man. Here we go!
[LEÓN yells]
You still fail to comprehend.
I cannot be slain boy.
[LEÓN grunting]
[ZARUBA]
León! The gate is closing!
[LEÓN gasps]
[MENDOZA]
And now what are you doing?
[ALFONSO] León! He means to
banish Mendoza to Makai!
Don't do it! You won't
be able to return!
León!
[MENDOZA]
Clever, aren't we?
You intend to keep me
here indefinitely?
Alas, that won't be so easy!
[LEÓN]
Uh!
I don't think so!
[MENDOZA] You do realize you'll
be trapped here as well?
[LEÓN]
It doesn't matter.
[MENDOZA]
Hmph.
Not a very fast learner,
I see. I told you I cannot--
[MENDOZA gasping]
[LEÓN roars]
What are you doing?
[MENDOZA screams]
[LEÓN grunts]
You are the epitome
of foolishness.
León!
[ALFONSO]
Miss Ema.
--Hold on.
--[EMA groans]
Listen, Alfonso!
I... If I lose consciousness,
just strike me until I awaken.
We cannot let this gate close.
León will be trapped
in Makai forever!
[ALFONSO]
Understood.
[MENDOZA] It appears your
idiotic friends beg to differ
on the issue of you
remaining here.
[MENDOZA]
Heh. Concede defeat.
Can you not see this
struggle is pointless?
Even if the gate closes,
for me it's merely a
matter of outliving you.
And so I shall. Before long,
some cretinous soul
will open another gate,
once more unleashing me
upon the world above.
[LEÓN]
The defeat is yours to concede.
I will die, but another
Knight will rise in my place.
And after him,
another, and another!
As long as the line
of Makai Knights
and their Alchemist
allies carries on,
you will never know freedom!
And someday, maybe
centuries from now,
maybe eons, they will find a way
to end you, once and for all!
If I cut the string,
it will all be over.
Witch's bastard.
[LEÓN]
Ema...
Alfonso...
[LEÓN screams]
[MENDOZA gasps]
[MENDOZA screams]
What is this flame?!
It scores me!
[MENDOZA]
You whore!
Uh!
[MENDOZA screams]
[ANNA]
León.
[LEÓN gasps]
Mother?!
[ANNA] Fear not.
Mendoza is helpless
to free himself from
the agony of my fire.
It shall engulf his
godlike form...
for all time.
Mother... why...?
[gasps]
[ANNA] It'll be all right.
Whatever life holds in store,
mother will be there
to protect you.
[GERMÁN]
Anna.
Give our precious son the
honor of carrying on this fight.
From me, he will have the
protection of loving fire.
Loving fire.
For all these years
I thought the flames
were stoked by revenge.
Mother...
Mother, forgive me!
My son.
Go now. You are needed
elsewhere. You've a duty
to fulfill. Never forget that
you are one who protects.
[gasps]
[ANNA] Know that beyond
all things, I love you.
Mother!
[GERMÁN] Moron don't look
back, it kills the moment.
--[GERMÁN chuckles]
--[LEÓN] Old man!
I knew you'd pull through in
the end, I'm proud of you.
Not that I expected any less
from the fruit of my loins.
[LEÓN gasps]
[gasps]
[GERMÁN]
Farewell, León
Father, don't leave.
Oh hell, I nearly forgot!
I need a favor.
Keep an eye on Ximena for me.
She's that innkeeper's daughter.
You don't mind, do ya?
Are you serious?! Unbelievable!
You're a scoundrel
to the very end.
--[ALFONSO] León!
--[LEÓN] Uh!
León!
[ALFONSO]
[BOTH laugh]
[LEÓN]
Ema! Alfonso!
[CITIZENS chatter]
[CITIZENS grumble]
[CITIZEN A] Look sharp!
It's His Highness, the prince!
Citizens, I wish to
thank you in person.
Your sweat and toil have
not gone unnoticed.
[WOMAN A]
Your Grace, if you please.
How fares His Majesty the King?
Well! A portion of his
strength returns each day.
I have no doubt your
reconstruction efforts
are what hasten his recovery.
[CITIZENS cheer]
Now, let us all do our utmost!
How may I be of
help to my people?
[YOUNG LADIES sing]
[CHAMBERLAIN, ALFONSO]
Uh?!
[YOUNG LADIES sing]
hose would be the daughters
of well-heeled aristocrats,
Your Grace. Please note how
they do not think it beneath
themselves to contribute.
Indeed, every soul in Santa Bard
is committed to rebuilding.
[YOUNG LADY A giggles]
[ALFONSO]
Ah!
[CHAMBERLAIN]
Ah, yes. Excellent choice.
Shall I enquire as
to her heraldry?
Uh, thank you, no! After
all, we've work to do.
[ALFONSO yelps]
[ALFONSO groans]
[ALFONSO gasps]
[LEÓN]
Well, Lara.
The chamomile flowers
have bloomed.
They're breathtaking.
Just as you said they'd be.
I hope you can see them.
Uh?
So you're going?
That's the intention, yes.
Except for some reason I'm
feeling a little homesick.
Why I long to stay somewhere
with such bad memories,
I can't say.
Huh, t'was only ever
a place to rest.
That it was.
I'd go with you if I could, but
I'm still needed around here.
Huh?! No one said anything about
you coming with me, jackass!
Oh, no of course.
I'll be seeing you.
Farewell.
[ZARUBA] Permit me to
ask as León's proxy.
Does the lady intend to return?
Hey! Don't speak for me!
Uh...
You'll be a fine man
someday, León. Take care.
[XIMENA]
Ah, hello. Welcome back.
Now that you're here I can
make preparations for dinner.
[LEÓN] Miss Ximena! What
is the meaning of this?!
I thought we agreed
you weren't to lug
heavy things around
unsupervised!
And Jiruba! I didn't
leave you with her
so you could be a piece
of costume jewelry!
She shouldn't be
pushing herself.
You may interpret my silence
to mean there is not a problem.
I choose to speak when
my words are necessary.
Calm down, León.
I'm more than equal to
a basket of laundry.
[JIRUBA] Already I have
pronounced too much.
I shall henceforth
utter no sound
until the inheritor of Zoro is
born. Tempt me not to speak.
Huh? Wait!
So it's going to be a boy?!
Jiruba! Come on!
Damn.
[XIMENA laughs]
Are you surprised?
Though boy or girl,
it matters little.
It is your father's child,
and for that, I am grateful.
Yes.
This time, father.
It is mine to pass down.
[GERMÁN]
León! Never forget...
[LEÓN] ...our duty as
protectors of this world!