[ESMERALDA] Alfonso has
grown into a fine young man.
A prince of the people
if there ever was one.
[GARCIA]
Your Highness!
[ALFONSO]
Mother!
Mendoza has betrayed our trust!
[HORROR SOLDIER groaning]
[gasps]
[ALFONSO, HORRO SOLDIER grunt]
[HORROR SOLDIER groans]
[HORROR SOLDIER growling]
[RAFAEL grunts]
--[RAFAEL grunts]
--[HORROR SOLDIER groans]
[ALFONSO gasps]
[ALFONSO] What manner
of creature are these?
'Tis plain they're not human!
If they answer to Mendosa
as you say, what is their aim?
What could they possibly want?
They are known as Horrors.
Creatures of the dark.
Beings of evil that
live to consume us.
Horrors, you say?
[RAFAEL] Mendoza exploits
a forbidden Madou device
that bridles and directs
Horrors to answer to his will.
The power it gives
him, he would use
to rule the kingdom
of Valiante unchallenged.
[ALFONSO gasps]
Very well, then!
You must lend me your strength,
that the villain may be stopped!
[RAFAEL]
Mm?
Sir, as heir apparent,
I have a duty to this land!
My mother needs me, as do the
folk who look to me for succor.
Yet, as I am, my skills
are unequal to the task.
I haven't the prowess to slay
these things as you do.
Please, sir, teach me
to drive these devils
back to the hell from whence
they came! [gasps]
[RAFAEL grunts]
--[HORROR SOLDIER grunts]
--[ALFONSO gasps]
How can you know the enemy
if you do not know yourself?
The truth must be
brought to light.
The truth of what?
I am Rafael Banderas, a friend,
of the late Golden Knight,
God rest his soul.
[RAFAEL] Where the human
heart embraces evil,
Horrors feast, possessing
those who invite them.
Such vile, poisonous creatures
have been hunted
since time out of mind.
Relentlessly pursued
by Men of the Armor:
The Makai Knights!
[GERMÁN chuckles] I wouldn't
touch that if I were you.
Oh! You are playing with fire!
What's that? Money?
Why, yes, of course
I'm good for it!
--[LEÓN] Disgusting man.
--[GERMÁN groans]
[LEÓN] Even your dreams
betray you for a letch.
Now, get up. We need
to eat breakfast.
How are you so full of vigor
this early in the morning?
[LEÓN] Unlike someone we know, I
go to bed at a reasonable hour.
Ah, yes, of course.
I see the logic.
If we must be prudent,
best get it over with now.
--[LEÓN grunts]
--[GERMÁN groans]
You, out of bed!
[gasps]
[LEÓN gasps]
[ZARUBA]
Golden Knight.
[ZARUBA] This is the day of the
New Moon. The Day of Promise!
An increment of your
life, has come due.
[LEÓN gasps]
[GERMÁN]
León!
What's wrong? Damn it,
boy, talk to me!
Wake up! León!
[sighs, gasps]
[RAFAEL] In ages past,
Horrors were a bane of which
every man, woman,
and child were aware.
Those who fought them
were lauded as heroes,
but time wore on,
and people forgot,
as they are wont to do.
Now those who fight Horrors
are persecuted as witches,
tortured, burned.
[ALFONSO grunts]
[RAFAEL] Your kingdom has
set its share of fires.
Violence against man
is forbidden to us.
Unable to defend themselves,
dozens, no, hundreds
of my comrades have lost their
lives to ignorance and ambition.
Yes, Mendoza had a
singular passion for
inciting hatred against witches.
Was that part of his plan?
Aye, he reviles our kind.
Knights, alchemists, allies.
He would have us, and
our kin, all murdered.
[ALFONSO] Then the Knight of
Light isn't just a legend,
he's real.
[RAFAEL]
The Golden Knight, Garo.
The blood that coursed through
his veins is within you.
[ALFONSO gasps]
But of course, there's
a new moon tonight.
[GERMÁN]
I should've known.
This is the one day
of the month when
the Golden Knight lies
in torpor. The day when
Madou Ring Zaruba claims a
portion of the vessel's life.
[sighs] And that's
all I can remember.
I should've asked your
mother for more detail.
[RAFAEL] The armor of a Makai
Knight is passed down by blood,
so it is with the Golden Knight.
Once there lived in
Valiante a witch,
sentenced by Mendoza to burn for
the crime of hexing the king.
In truth, she was
a Makai Alchemist,
and she carried within her the
grandson of the Golden Knight.
Even as she died,
she gave birth.
An infant emerged
from the flames.
Thus the Golden Knight's
bloodline survived.
I know the story well.
A man rescued the boy,
and there's been no sign
of either of them since
that fateful day, long ago.
[RAFAEL]
Yet as it happens,
the child was not
the woman's only kin.
She also had a sister.
[ALFONSO]
What were their names?
Anna Luis. She was
the condemned.
Her younger sibling...
[RAFAEL]
...Esmeralda.
[gasps]
Anna Luis held a sacred duty,
to fight as a Makai Alchemist,
but also to continue
her father's bloodline,
so that his golden armor
could be passed down.
Esmeralda was
adopted by nobility,
spared the life of a warrior.
She lived happily, her
every need attended to.
[RAFAEL] She's a fine woman,
but she's lived in ignorance:
of her elder sister, of Horrors,
of the truth of her own birth.
[ALFONSO gasps]
She was kept unaware.
Only two people knew the secret,
myself and the
man who possessed
the golden armor of old.
Your own grandfather.
Mother wore this from
the time she was a girl.
She said it acted as a kind
of protective talisman,
but she didn't
know against what.
After Anna's son inherited
the Golden Armor,
my role consisted
in keeping vigil.
To watch from the shadows.
Only if misfortune befell
you was I to make
my presence known.
[gasps]
Mendosa now realizes
you're of the blood.
His hatred of the Makai Knights
cannot be overstated,
believe you me.
Hence the man's mendacity.
Please, you must answer me this,
if I am indeed descended
from the blood of those
who fight Horrors,
this means that I too have
the power to defeat them?
[RAFAEL]
Mm.
[ALFONSO gasps]
[ALFONSO grunting]
[ALFONSO yells]
[ALFONSO groaning]
[ALFONSO pants]
[RAFAEL]
Mm.
[ALFONSO panting]
I've met with worse.
You can certainly stand
your ground against men.
[ALFONSO grunts]
Hear me.
Whether I possess a shred of
power against the Horrors,
or would succumb to them.
To protect my people I will
give all that I have!
My life, included!
[RAFAEL]
Hm.
[ALFONSO gasps]
[RAFAEL]
Strong though it is,
blood alone cannot
carry the day.
[ALFONSO gasps]
You have heart,
but as you are now, you
cannot even don the armor.
No price is too steep,
no sacrifice too dear!
[RAFAEL]
So you say.
[ALFONSO gasps]
[OCTAVIA]
Oh, Fernando.
How peacefully you
sleep yet again today.
That's right, Your Highness,
loyal Octavia is here to give
serenity to your slumber.
She'll remain by your
side, come what may.
[FERNANDO groans]
[gasps]
[MENDOZA]
How fares his Majesty?
[OCTAVIA] The medicine seems to
be working quite well, sir.
[MENDOZA]
Mind you mix it carefully,
'tis not yet the time for our
king to leave the stage.
[OCTAVIA]
Quite.
[MENDOZA]
What of the Queen?
[OCTAVIA] She has been
vigorously questioned.
The interrogators are
confident of her ignorance.
[OCTAVIA] She knows
nothing of her pedigree.
What would you
have me do with her?
She can be made to
disappear at our leisure.
Let her live for the time being.
She may yet prove
useful against her son.
Very well, as you wish.
[MENDOZA]
Mm.
Your will be done in
perpetuity, my master.
[RAFAEL]
My pardon from the Vatican.
As he says.
My word. Connections
to the Vatican, sir?
That is impressive.
[RAFAEL]
Thank the forger.
[gasps]
[RAFAEL] Your grandfather
excelled in battle as few men
before him, a warrior
from head to toe.
However, a worldly
man he was not.
Concealing your mother's
origins fell to me.
I personally arranged
her adoption by nobility.
Your grandfather hadn't
the nuance for such things.
Not that I orchestrated her
ascension to Queen, mind you.
That twist of fate
surprised even me.
[ALFONSO]
I see.
May I ask where we're going?
[RAFAEL]
Valdona.
Count Romero's domain.
Do you know of it?
[ALFONSO] Of course. The Land
of Grapes, they call it.
'Tis said the soil is so rich,
the vine cannot help but thrive.
[RAFAEL]
I suggest you look more closely.
So barren.
[ALFONSO]
Pardon me.
[VILLAGERS gasp]
[ALFONSO] Might I ask
something of you good people?
[VILLAGERS scream]
[RAFAEL]
Circumstances, namely you,
led me from my intended path.
This was to be my
original destination.
But, sir, Count Romero is held
in great esteem far and wide.
He is a lover of
music and literature,
the proud patron
of many an artist.
I'm sure that was all
true at some point.
However, the man of integrity
is now something else.
[RAFAEL]
Today is the New Moon.
Mind you step cautiously.
[ALFONSO gasping]
[gasps]
[HORROR SOLDIER grunts]
[ALFONSO]
Ah!
[bell rings]
[gasps]
Look, a Horror.
[HORROR SOLDIER laughs]
[HORROR SOLDIER roars]
[RAFAEL]
Stay back, lad.
Quickly, Sir Rafael!
Use your armor!
[HORROR SOLDIER grunting]
[RAFAEL]
Not yet.
--[HORROR SOLDIER growls]
--[RAFAEL grunts]
[RAFAEL grunts]
[ALFONSO groans]
[ALFONSO groaning]
[MALE VILLAGER humming]
--[FEMALE VILLAGER sobbing]
--[BABY cries]
[ALFONSO yells]
[ALFONSO grunts]
[ALFONSO gasps]
[MALE VILLAGER gasping]
[BABY cries]
[ALFONSO gasps]
Monster!
[ALFONSO grunts]
Die, die, die, die!
--[ALFONSO grunts]
--[FEMALE VILLAGER screams]
[ALFONSO groans]
[yells]
[RAFAEL grunts]
[ALFONSO gasping]
[RAFAEL]
Gaia, Knight of Defense.
Go forth!
[RAFAEL grunts]
[ALFONSO gasping]
[RAFAEL]
Mm.
[FEMALE VILLAGER sobs]
I am so sorry. So very sorry.
--Please forgive me.
--[BABY cries]
I beg you, teach me.
I have seen what it
is to fight Horrors, sir.
And I will do whatever I must
to take up arms against them.
My people need a warrior.
Sir Rafael, please,
mold me as you will!
So be it, then.
From this moment forward,
you'll come to know all that
falls within my power to teach.
[ALFONSO grunts]
[LEÓN]
Where am I?
[PREVIOUS GARO] A world apart
from the ebb and flow of time.
[LEÓN gasps]
[PREVIOUS GARO] According to
the contract of the New Moon,
Zaruba devoured a
single day of your life.
You stand now in the place where
that deficit of time lingers.
[LEÓN]
I don't...
I don't think I understand.
[PREVIOUS GARO]
Past. Present. Future.
Here, they are indistinguishable
from one another.
They flow as one.
[LEÓN grunts, gasps]
Are you--?
[PREVIOUS GARO] Do not fear
your flame, Young Garo.
Let it burn.
When you are lost,
consult your blade.
Ask it, "Who is it
I must protect?"
[LEÓN]
Who is it I must protect?
[PREVIOUS GARO] Therein lies
the answer to everything.
[gasps]
[LEÓN grunts]
[GERMÁN] A-ha! The
sleeper awakes, does he?
These kind folks were good
enough to offer us a ride.
What, are you still groggy?
Go on, thank them!
[FEMALE TRAVELER giggles]
[LEÓN]
Did, did my...
[GERMÁN]
Hm?
It's nothing. Never mind.
[GERMÁN]
Spit it out, m'boy!
There'so point in
being such a cipher.
It's unhealthy,
bottling one's emotions.
This age belongs
to the unfettered!
Sure. Whatever.
[MALE TRAVELER] There she is,
gentlemen: the Mond River.
Cross that, an' we'll
be in Sahnta Bard.
[GERMÁN]
We've made it.
[LEÓN grunts]
[GARM] A man who once
called himself friend.
Now a light extinguished.
What depths of night
do those eyes reflect?