[GAEL] I will employ all of
my remaining power to see
the Madou ring made whole again.
[GERMÁN]
León! He's one of them!
[ZARUBA]
My name is Zaruba.
When Garo came
to be, thus did I.
[EMA] Perhaps our paths will
cross again in Santa Bard.
[ALFONSO gasps]
I defy you in the
name of Valiante!
Know you this, demon!
[ALFONSO groans]
[gasps]
In such armor, he's an echo of
Valiante's legendary savior:
The Knight of Light!
Hurry up, let's go.
[gasps]
[RAFAEL] Where the human heart
embraces evil, Horrors feast,
possessing those
who invite them.
Such vile, poisonous creatures
have been hunted
since time out of mind.
Relentlessly pursued
by Men of the Armor:
The Makai Knights!
[LEÓN] Old man. Wait,
where are we going?
Hey, are you listening to me?
--[GERMÁN] No. Come again?
--[LEÓN] Of course you're not.
[LEÓN]
Where are we even headed?
These woodlands are far off
from our original route.
Oh, you noticed that, did you?
Well, then, suppose I'd
best keep you informed.
There's a village nearby,
lots of dark rumors
have come out of late.
The map says we should
be right on top of it.
This is waste of our time.
No harm in taking
a quick peek, Leon.
But you're always going on
about our sacred mission
to vanquish Horrors.
How it's our knightly duty.
[GERMÁN laughs] All right, son.
Heed your father's wisdom.
Sacred missions are all
well and good, my boy,
but sampling the wine and women
of small country towns,
these are the moments you
treasure for a lifetime.
[LEÓN grunts]
[barking]
[GERMÁN] Now this is
the true countryside.
[LEÓN sighs]
Well this place doesn't
even have a bar!
How's a man supposed
to sample the wine?
[GERMÁN]
Good day, young miss.
Ha, ha, ha!
Ee!
Guess you won't be sampling any
of the local women, either.
[GERMÁN chuckles]
[VILLAGE CHIEF] Your raiment
would name you as travelers.
I am known as the mayor
of our tucked away haven.
What brings you so far afield?
Ah, well met.
[VILLAGE CHIEF grunts]
[GERMÁN]
My son and I are mere pilgrims,
traveling to the Holy Land.
Some small piece of
gossip drew us here.
[laughs] Rumors of the
mysterious always
pique our curiosity.
[VILLAGE CHIEF] It seems
this small gossip of yours
has led you astray. Ours is
a simple village that keeps to
a simple faith. We know
little misfortune here.
Oh? We had heard whisperings
of strange disappearances.
A monk and a church official,
if I recall it true.
No such thing, good sir,
you must have been mistaken.
Truth be told, it is the sudden
appearance of wandering folk
that drives our citizens back
to the safety of their homes.
Travelers are often known
to bring ill fortune.
I must insist you
be on your way.
[GERMÁN]
Heh.
[LEÓN exhales]
It appears your leads
were wrong this time.
Come on, let's get outta here.
Why so eager to put
this place behind you?
[LEÓN]
You should know best.
[GERMÁN]
Don't go on about revenge again.
God above!
Sometimes I think you've
been replaced by a Horror!
[gasps] Have you?
[LEÓN gasps]
Get off!
[GERMÁN] This drive for
vengeance will tear you apart.
If you insist on getting torn
to shreds, it's much more fun
if you let women do the honors.
[LEÓN grunts]
[GERMÁN]
Huh?
[BOY A] Hey, maybe you didn't
get it after last time,
you gotta pay the toll if you
ever trespass over here again!
[BOY B]
You scared now, boy?
Got no more smart comebacks?
[BOY C] We'll take
that stupid doll first!
Give it here!
I said give it to me!
[BOY C groans]
What'd he do? What happened?
Damn!
[gasps]
[LEÓN]
Let him go!
Three on one's kind of unfair.
[BOY A] We weren't gonna
do nothin' to the kid.
Oh, I think you were.
Maybe we'll jump in and
even up the numbers a bit,
what do ya think boys?
You should leave this
place while you can.
That's right, the whole
village has been cursed.
His mom's an evil witch who
cast a spell on this place!
If you don't get the hell out,
you'll be her next victims!
[BOYS chuckle]
Guess the village has
a mystery after all.
You snapped at the hand
of that mean bully.
Thank you.
It's late.
We'll take you back home,
if you show us the way.
[ALOIS]
I'm back.
Alois? Welcome home!
[gasps]
[AURELIA]
Oh! And who are these two?
[ALOIS] They saved my doll
and me from the other boys.
Did they now? I do hope you
said thank you, Alois.
[AURELIA sighs]
[GERMÁN clears throat]
[GERMÁN]
He seems a good boy,
if perhaps a little impetuous.
Truth be told, he only
began acting so heedlessly
after his father passed.
Since then, the only company
he's kept is with that doll
he found in the forest.
Ah, I am grateful, and very
sorry for the trouble, good sir.
Come, none of that.
Call me Germán.
This is my son, León.
I am Aurelia.
So, a pilgrimage
brings you hence?
[GERMÁN]
Yes and no.
We heard some kind of curse
had befallen the area,
so we thought,
"that's worth a look."
[bell chimes]
[AURELIA]
Ah, you're both witch hunters.
[GERMÁN grunts]
The townsfolk told you I was
some kind of sorceress.
Please, worry not.
I have no curses at my disposal.
Seems only fair to tell you,
my charm is often
called quite bewitching.
[AURELIA laughs]
Are you certain you're a pilgrim
and not a jester, Germán?
[GERMÁN]
Eh? Touché.
[AURELIA] I'm happy to offer
you a place by the fire.
You won't find similar welcome
elsewhere in town, I fear.
Oh! That would be wonderful.
I've spent many nights outside,
nodding off to my son's griping.
[LEÓN]
Mm.
[BOY A] Y'know, better
not be lying to us.
[BOY B] You said a band
of thieves hid all their
treasure somewhere out here.
[BOY C] He's not lying if he
knows what's good for him!
[BOY A]
Wait!
You brought us to the swamp?
This place is haunted!
Uh! He's right!
Mama said to never to
come out here after dark!
--[creaking]
--[BOYS gasp]
[BOYS scream]
[GERMÁN] Why would folks
think you're a witch?
They've always been
untrusting because
I wasn't born in this village.
My husband was a wanderer,
and one day we settled here.
After he was taken from us,
all manner of ill
fortune befell the town.
I'm sure the
disappearances don't help.
[AURELIA] True. Nothing
remains of them afterwards,
it's as though they've
fallen into the ether.
That's what happened
to the lad's father?
[AURELIA]
No.
He was set upon
by a band of thieves,
on the road to the capital.
That hardly seems enough
to name you a sorceress.
[AURELIA]
I am easy to hate.
They need someone to
heap their scorn upon.
Why not the outsider? The one
who never truly belonged.
Why did the Mayor try
so hard to deceive us?
He decried the
disappearances as rumor.
[GERMÁN] He was trying
very hard to hide something,
tossing us out the way he did.
[AURELIA gasps]
[door opens]
[VILLAGERS shouting]
[GERMÁN grunts]
[AURELIA gasps]
Heathen witch!
Give me back my son!
How many children must
you take from us?
Return my boy to me right now!
Give him back! Tell me where
you took my child, sorceress!
[GERMÁN]
Breathe, everyone.
I'm sure this is just
a misunderstanding
that we can all work out.
[VILLAGE CHIEF]
Well, well.
Your presence here
does explain quite a bit.
The she-devil saw fit
to summon help.
Now then, the truth.
If some children are missing,
we want to help search for them.
Why don't you tell
us what you know?
[MOTHER] We know that
the witch's child led them
into the forest! He was seen!
[AURELIA]
My son hasn't left our home!
[MOTHER]
Stop your filthy lying!
[GERMÁN] I assure you, the boy's
been here all evening.
[MOTHER B]
You're no better than her!
Step back, rest your
anger, and consider,
you told us that this was
a village of faith, sir.
And I tell you now that this
is a village matter.
Be silent and do not
interfere with things
well beyond your knowing.
Take her now.
She will soon confess.
Stop this!
Easy.
--[ALOIS whimpering]
--Now, come along!
[screams]
[grunts]
--[ALOIS panting]
--[MAN] Get back here!
[groans]
My apologies. These
longs legs are a curse.
León.
You handle him and I'll
make sure Aurelia's safe.
[LEÓN]
Mm.
[VILLAGE CHIEF]
It's about time you
started telling us the truth.
You called them here.
[VILLAGE CHIEF]
They just happened to come
to our village, then? What did
you tell them of the ceremony?
[AURELIA]
I told them nothing, I swear it!
[VILLAGE CHIEF]
Hm.
[AURELIA cries]
[VILLAGE CHIEF]
I'll ask you one more time.
What did you tell
them of the ceremony?
[door creaks]
Come quickly!
Sir, your home burns!
[VILLAGERS murmur]
We're fighting the flames
as best we can,
but hell itself seems
to stoke them on!
He did this. In his
final breaths, a curse.
--[bell rings]
--[VILLAGERS murmur]
No, please!
[GERMÁN]
It's me.
[AURELIA sighs]
Are you all right?
[AURELIA]
Yes.
[GERMÁN]
Hm.
[GERMÁN, AURELIA gasp]
What were you planning to do
with the witch, pray tell?
[AURELIA gasps]
That depends on what you
planned to do with her.
You cretins clearly have no idea
how to properly treat a lady.
[grunting] Uh?
Tell me, where is your son?
[GERMÁN] He must have just
wandered off somewhere.
That boy's quite
a handful, you see.
Best not worry about him.
[VILLAGE CHIEF]
Yes, of course,
just an old man's
idle curiosity.
Now, perhaps it would be best if
you escorted Miss Aurelia home.
All suspicions have
been put to rest.
[GERMÁN]
Hm.
[VILLAGE CHIEF]
Prepare the ceremony.
It must be tonight.
[LEÓN gasping]
[ALOIS]
Yes, I'm safe.
Please, tell me how I can
protect my mother.
Those people, they...
[LEÓN grunts]
[LEÓN gasps]
Alois. Good, you're all right.
I was worried about you.
Come, let us go.
Where's my mother?
[LEÓN] Don't you worry, my old
man promised that he would
take care of it. He may be
a fool, but he's no liar.
[ALOIS]
What do you think?
Very well.
[LEÓN]
Why did you run so far?
[ALOIS] The villagers never
go there because it's haunted.
I knew it'd be safe.
[LEÓN]
Who's home was it?
[ALOIS]
An old woodcutter's.
He was the person
the villagers used to hate.
[LEÓN]
And, where is he now?
[ALOIS]
Why did you come here?
[LEÓN]
Hm?
[ALOIS] Why did you come
to this forgotten village?
Because we think that something
here is hurting innocent people.
It's our job to
put an end to it.
[ALOIS] Like what? Like the
people who killed my father?
[LEÓN]
No.
We aren't bounty hunters who can
chase after any common brigand.
I'm sorry.
[ALOIS] See? I told you
they didn't know.
[LEÓN grunts]
[GERMÁN grunts, gasps]
[GERMÁN]
All of them are clean.
Not pure, but there's
no Horror among them.
Which can mean only one thing.
[LEÓN grunts]
Can't be him.
[GERMÁN]
Let me finish this.
I wouldn't want you to
have to cut down a child.
[LEÓN]
Then don't treat me like one!
A Horror must be ended, be it
in the form of a man or a boy.
[GERMÁN]
I hope you have the strength.
[bell rings]
[LEÓN]
No response.
None at all.
If it's not him, all that
remains is a force from
outside the village.
[LEÓN]
Miss Aurelia?
[AURELIA]
Mm?
[LEÓN]
What of the woodcutter?
[gasps]
I found Alois at a
hut in the forest.
When I asked, he told me it was
once the home of a woodsman.
[AURELIA] The villagers
called it an exorcism.
They claimed it would purify
our land, our misfortunes.
[LEÓN grunts]
Leon, what is it?
The Horror is inside his doll.
[AURELIA]
Where is my son?
My Alois?
[AURELIA]
[GERMÁN grunts]
[AURELIA gasps]
[DOLL BOY] Hurry! We have to
get as far away as we can!
Those men just
wanna take me away!
I won't let them have you!
[DOLL BOY]
Then do just as I tell you!
Come on, faster!
Alois, listen, you have
to hand it over.
Trust me. It's deceiving
you.
Trying to use you to harm
the others in the village.
Give me the doll,
and I'll destroy it.
[LEÓN grunts]
[HORROR DOLL BOY grunts]
[ALOIS gasps]
[LEÓN yells]
[LEÓN grunting]
[HORROR DOLL BOY groans]
[LEÓN yells]
[LEÓN gasps]
--[HORROR DOLL BOY roars]
--[LEÓN grunts]
[LEÓN]
Out of the way!
Never!
They took away my papa,
and they deserve to die!
[gasps]
[ALOIS] Why should they get
to live when he's gone?
Why?
[GERMÁN grunts]
[AURELIA]
My husband.
He was a part of
that dreadful night!
But he knew it to be wrong
when they first began it.
He tried. He wanted to tell
the Church what they had done.
[ALOIS]
I saw them do it.
He ran for the church, but they
hunted him down in the woods.
[ALOIS gasps]
[ALOIS]
They called him a traitor,
said the price of
our lives was his own.
I'll hurt them all!
I have to hurt them.
I want my papa back!
Alois, don't think like that.
I know it hurts.
[cries] I knew something
had changed in him.
He's my son. My son.
You invited us to stay
the night because
you suspected something.
Alois was changing.
So you needed us
to help stop him
from succumbing to the Horror.
[GERMÁN gasps]
Seems we have an unwanted guest.
[MALE VILLAGER gasps]
[HORROR DOLL BOY, MALE
VILLAGERS grunt]
[GERMÁN]
Guess León didn't kill it.
[VILLAGERS gasping]
[VILLAGERS scream]
[VILLAGE CHIEF gasping]
[VILLAGE CHIEF screams]
[LEÓN grunts]
[HORROR DOLL BOY growls]
[LEÓN grunting]
[HORROR DOLL BOY roars]
[VILLAGE CHIEF whines]
[LEÓN grunts]
[HORROR DOLL BOY groans]
[HORROR DOLL BOY groaning]
[LEÓN yells]
[ALOIS]
Please, no!
[LEÓN gasps]
[HORROR DOLL BOY groans]
[ALOIS crying]
[AURELIA]
Alois.
Mother's here. I'm so sorry.
I can't bring your father back.
Forgive me.
[ALOIS wails]
Safe travels.
[LEÓN]
It's not right.
Let it be, son.
It's hard to protect man if you
know the darkness in him.
[GARM]
Heart forged of tempered steel.
Body encased in armor.
The flint struck for golden
flame, to banish the dark.