[NICHOLAS]
Oh, I see.
I take it you're
a Makai Alchemist?
[EMA]
Tell me something, you wretch.
Does the name Luciano
mean anything to you?
[LEÓN] I thought you
hated us Makai Knights.
Oh, I do. Especially those
who've only seen a bared breast
while they're nursing.
[GARM] Will you continue
your own search?
Then may your quest bear fruit.
[EMA] Besides, I know
the thing I'm hunting
won't be found in Santa Bard.
Hunting, you say?
I've a Horror in mind.
[GERMÁN] I have to say,
a fine thing it is
to have you back in
the thick of it with us.
Actually.
My orders involve yours
truly serving Mendoza
for the foreseeable future.
[gasps]
[LEÓN]
What's the meaning of this?
[ALFONSO]
Oracle, please!
He asked you a question!
What in God's name
would possess my old man
to align himself with Mendoza?
How does the serpent still
live?!
And why weren't we
told this before?!
We have the right to an answer.
I cannot for the life of me
conceive of exoneration
for such a villian.
I see that the Golden
Armor has returned itself
to its prior bearer.
Stop dodging the issue.
[ZARUBA]
It is fruitless, León.
Garm is not to be pried.
She discloses only that which
she wishes to disclose.
Ah, incidentally,
there's another matter the
two of you know nothing of.
Dear, Ema Guzmán.
Very soon... she is
going to meet her demise.
[EMA]
It's almost time, Luciano.
Almost time.
[ALFONSO]
Her blatancy rattles me.
Though 'tis clear Garm
is merely attempting
to deflect our misgivings.
Yes, but it's equally clear
we can't abandon Ema
to face her doom.
I'm aware of that.
Garm is a damnably
effective manipulator.
[ALFONSO grunts]
Leave it to me, Alfonso.
You dare not stray away
from the castle for any
great length of time.
However, I'm free to
go wherever I please.
Would that I could join you.
I'll endeavor to shed more light
on your father and
Mendoza in your absence.
Best of luck to you.
You as well, cousin.
Godspeed your search.
Oh my, you're a pretty one
to look at, aren't you?
Hello.
[PROSTITUTE chuckles]
[PROSTITUTE] Care for
a spot of fun, stranger?
I can see that you're
new to these streets.
Pray tell, where
do you come from?
[MAN]
The sky.
Oh. I see.
Uh.
[PROSTITUTE grunts]
Every one of them is gone.
Save for my own,
not a soul is left.
[EMA]
Pay more mind to what you eat.
You'll get sick.
[PROSTITUTE gasps]
Hello, Luciano.
[LUCIANO]
I thought you'd never find me.
Hello, Ema.
[PROSTITUTE]
Uh...
What is this?
Ugh. Devil take you both!
I have waited ages for you
to track me down, love.
Sorry to keep you waiting.
That said, you
shouldn't have worried.
Whatever else I may be,
I'm a woman of my word.
[LUCIANO]
You look a touch... haggard.
[EMA] You look exactly the same
as the last time I saw you.
Well done.
Ha. Don't be thick. Where do
you think you're going?
It's no use, darling,
my net already has you.
Beautiful girl.
[gasps]
[EMA growls, yells]
[EMA]
Luciano!
[LUCIANO]
Ema.
[LEÓN]
Ema!
[LEÓN screaming]
[EMA]
Luciano, no!
Are you all right, Ema?
[EMA groaning]
[LEÓN]
Uh.
You meddling son of a bitch.
Do you have any idea
what you've just done?!
I never asked for
your help, León.
Damn you! I finally
had the bastard!
I can't believe it.
Years of my life spent
searching, and you--
[EMA crying]
[LEÓN] I-I'm sorry.
I was only trying to--
[EMA]
Get away from me!
Rob someone else
of their purpose!
Please, I--
[ZARUBA] I've put a marker
on the Horror just engaged.
Now, wherever he runs, wherever
he hides, it is no matter.
Sooner or later the net
will close on our quarry.
[EMA]
Ah, I see.
So, in the end,
the armor returned to
the original bearers.
Good for you and Alfonso.
[LEÓN]
Garm told us about you.
Said you were hell-bent on
tracking a particular Horror.
That you were willing
to sacrifice your life
to destroy him.
Quite the gossip, that Garm.
But this is none
of your business.
We've had this discussion.
I trust Makai Knights about
as far as I can throw them.
I know you don't
think much of me.
Even so, surely you can
use Zaruba's information.
[EMA]
Uh.
Then lets speak in terms
of quid pro quo.
Luciano location, you tell
me what Zaruba finds out.
And in exchange, I'll
offer something you need.
Fair enough, except...
I need nothing.
Don't play games with me, chico.
There can be no trade
if you need nothing.
There must be
something you desire.
What about my body?
Perhaps even my life?
[gasps]
Though, of course,
I'll thank you to wait
till I've vanquished Luciano
for that particular privilege.
No. You know what?
I'll yield Zaruba's information
in exchange for the reasons
behind what you're doing.
[EMA gasps]
[ZARUBA] The Horror's name
is Luciano Guzmán.
I know more than
his whereabouts.
In fact, I know a
great deal more.
I'd be happy to tell you
why this woman is
so obsessed with him--
Like hell!
Ow! Hey! Let go!
Either give me the dignity
of telling you myself,
or the deal's off. I won't
be spoken for by jewelry.
I take umbrage at that
statement, Alchemist.
I am a Madou Ring.
His name is, in fact,
Luciano Guzmán.
He was a Makai
Alchemist of great skill.
And for a fleeting
moment, my husband.
My beautiful girl.
[HORROR A roaring]
[HORROR B groaning]
[MAKAI KNIGHT B]
Much obliged for the help!
[MAKAI KNIGHT C] We'll be
takin' it from here, thank you.
No offense, but you first
liners oughta stand back.
We'll handle the
warrior part,
you put your feet up
in the Watchdog Center.
[BOTH laughing]
[HORROR C roaring]
[slap]
[WOMAN] He's dead!
How could you?!
You vowed to deliver us from
this fate! You're a monster!
What you've done
is unforgivable!
We did everything we could.
There was no saving the man.
Once a Horror, there
is no hope of return.
I'm very sorry.
You at least were saved. Yes?
For that much I am grateful.
[WOMAN]
Don't touch me!
What is the point of living
if my love is dead?!
I can't face my
life without him.
He was my entire world!
[WOMAN crying]
[MAKAI KNIGHT A] And, of
course, that Luciano fellow
is brooding again.
He's still convinced
there must be some way
to keep human beings
from becoming Horrors,
in lieu of hunting them.
Many a mind has
pondered the question
before that damned fool.
If there was a way, we'd
have discovered it long ago.
[MAKAI KNIGHT A] Yes, precisely.
That's my entire point.
There are limits to what
even the most accomplished
of Alchemists can do.
Horrors are dealt with by steel,
not academic chin stroking.
[HORROR D]
You cannot save them.
Toil as you might,
they are a lost cause.
You grapple with
an impossibility.
They cannot be saved.
The world is
shrouded in darkness
and there is nothing to be done.
In the end, we're
only saving those
who've yet to become
Horrors themselves.
[LUCIANO]
If all we do is kill,
those we vow to protect
eventually become our quarry.
If a Horror can be
changed back however...
Yes, yes. I know.
I'm an incurable romantic.
But I have to believe
there's a spell
that can keep the Horrors
from getting a foothold.
You'll find it one day.
[WOMAN]
He's dead! How could you?!
[EMA]
Luciano!
It landed over there!
[WOMAN] Monster! What
you've done is unforgivable!
[LUCIANO]
I'm sorry. I'm so sorry.
[HORROR D]
Too bad. Another one fallen.
Again you must kill
whom you wish to save.
[EMA]
Luciano. You have to stop.
This isn't your fault.
There's no reason we
have to keep doing this.
We can carve out a new
life somewhere else.
We can walk away.
Lay down our weapons.
Grow old together.
Doesn't that sound nice?
[LUCIANO]
Thank you, Ema.
But... I cannot let this
have been for nothing.
[EMA]
Luciano?
[LUCIANO]
This view.
From here, it looks as
though everyone is gone.
Odd that is should be...
such a comforting thought.
Luciano... No... Please...
[MAKAI KNIGHT C]
Beyond pathetic!
What have I always said about
the blasted Makai Alchemists?
They're only one step removed
from Horrors themselves.
Don't worry, Ema Guzmán, you did
well in coming to us with this.
Even as we speak,
our comrades in arms
are leaving no stone
unturned in their search.
Thank you, sir.
Now, I would like to join them
without delay. He's my husband.
I feel it only proper that I
should be the one to seal him.
Not only is there
no need, it's unwise.
Because Luciano Guzmán
is your husband,
you stand a great chance of
becoming a Horror yourself
before this is over.
I'm afraid we've little choice
but to restrain you
for the time being.
This is absurd! For God's
sake, I know my heart!
You can't imprison me!
No, wait! Please!
You don't understand!
I made him a solemn vow!
[MAKAI KNIGHT C] You're not
fit to take down a Horror
either way.
[MAKAI KNIGHT A]
Leave it to us.
This is what we do.
[MAKAI KNIGHT B]
Arrogant wench.
I suggest you learn your place.
[EMA]
It is clear I cannot rely
on the power of
the Makai Knights.
I must end this myself...
as I promised.
[EMA] The Horror that played
on Luciano's despair must die.
By my hands alone.
[EMA]
The search has taken years,
but I finally tracked
him here to Paolagena.
And this is where
it all has to end.
I would gladly kill you before
I let you interfere again.
I didn't come here to serve
a Horror our kind of justice.
I came to protect
the townspeople
and, incidentally, you.
I've offered up my reasons
for hunting Luciano.
So, we'll set out on the morrow.
[LEÓN]
Good.
[EMA panting, groaning]
You've come to save
me from myself. Well..
Could it be our angry little
chico has grown up at last?
[clanking]
[EMA]
León!
What the hell are you
doing just standing there?
The least you could do is help.
[LEÓN] Oh, sure.
Like I'd fall for that.
If I tried, you'd only get mad.
[EMA] Ha. Very good.
You're starting to learn.
He keeps coming here. I can't
figure out why he would though.
I know. This place
isn't special to him.
So as to what draws him,
your guess is as good as mine.
[LEÓN]
Ema.
[EMA]
Hm?
I give my word that
I have no intention
of coming between
the two of you.
However, should he turn
his attention on the town,
my hand will be forced.
I'd expect no less of you.
[ZARUBA]
He is here.
[grunts]
Careful, Ema.
[EMA grunts]
[EMA yelps]
Like hell I'll let you
fly where you please!
[EMA groaning]
[EMA gasps]
[screaming]
[EMA]
Luciano!
[LEÓN]
Ema!
[LUCIANO]
Welcome home, my darling.
I've searched for so long.
I should've known
you'd come back here.
Back to our home.
Where we were always
so happy together.
[LUCIANO]
Yes.
Yes, exactly.
I can't bear to lose
you a second time.
Oh, Ema.
You shall be within me forever.
Indeed. To eternity and back.
Rest in peace, dear Luciano.
Know I love you.
[thud]
[EMA]
Léon! Another!
Now, damn you!
[EMA groaning]
[EMA]
Hey...
What's the matter?
Can't you hear?
You have a fever.
You don't need another
drink. You need rest.
[EMA]
Ugh. Cabrón!
Don't tell me what I
need! I'm celebrating!
Now! Another! Immediately!
I won't ask you again!
[LEÓN]
Stop!
You'll tear the
stitches wide open!
And you reek!
[EMA]
Cállate, chico!
Dammit, Ema!
[EMA cyring]
[LEÓN] Talk to me.
Where are you in pain?
[EMA]
It's finally over.
[LEÓN]
Yes, finally.
Luciano has found his peace.
Get some rest. Everything will
be all right now, I promise.
[EMA crying]
Don't you dare!
You were a child the
last time I saw you
and now you talk to me
like an goddamned adult?!
[gasps]
[crying]
[LEÓN]
Uh!
--[LEÓN grunts]
--[EMA gasps]
[GARM] It is no small thing,
putting one's trust in another.
Having done so, all roads
lead to the same end.