[MENDOZA] It seems the creation
of our knights continues apace.
[JORDI]
Armor dark as the abyss.
Cut a dire figure, he did.
Folks took to calling
him the Black Knight.
[BERNARDO]
The choreography of his blade.
I know it from a lifetime ago.
[BERNARDO chuckles]
Of course.
[GERMÁN humming]
[LEÓN]
Hey.
When are we going to
storm the castle already?
C'mon! There's no point
in being hasty!
We still don't know
what we're up against.
For now, we wait for the ladies
to dig up more information.
God forbid you ask beyond
the walls of the brothel!
[chuckles] Horrors
tend to manifest
where passions run highest.
It's a dirty job, but, ha.
Really?
Then what's with
the fancy mirror?
Is it part of your arsenal?
So to speak.
There's not a woman alive
who'd spurn a gift.
It renders them zealous.
Fatherly wisdom!
You'll understand when
you're older, son.
[LEÓN]
You jackass!
Are you ever not thinking
with your codpiece?
[GERMÁN groans]
And that is how your
most lovely gift
met its sad demise.
A tragic tale to be sure,
but not half as tragic
as this son of yours.
No, no, no, no, no.
That's enough about him.
Though I do know another
little boy of mine
that understands
your special gift.
Quite enough!
--You cheeky rogue.
--[rattling]
[SOLDIER 8A]
Circle 'round! He was wounded!
He won't get far like that!
What the hell's
going on out there?
I wonder who they're
chasing down this time.
The soldiers always seem
to be after some witch.
[GERMÁN]
Hm...
[PROSTITUTE 8A] Maybe one day
they'll hunt girls like me.
Name me a witch who deceives men
with her pretty words
and her soft kisses.
I wonder if I would survive it.
They'll have to send eunuchs
to capture you, my dear.
Flattery earns you no extra.
But I must say there is
something oddly appealing
about a man in armor.
Bound up so tight.
Maybe so, but, dear heart,
all of my best battles
were fought completely naked!
[PROSTITUTE 8A laughs] Naughty
boy! I'll show you a battle!
[GERMÁN]
However will I take victory?
I've a sharp sword but no armor!
[RAFAEL] Where the human
heart embraces evil,
Horrors feast, possessing
those who invite them.
Such vile, poisonous
creatures have been hunted
since time out of mind,
relentlessly pursued
by Men of the Armor.
The Makai Knights!
[GERMÁN yawns]
Ew... I'll never hear
the end of it from León
if I show up like this.
Better avoid him.
Huh?
[IRENE panting]
[IRENE yelps]
Running awfully quick,
wouldn't you say?
Please, help! I beg of you!
Don't let them take me!
Huh?
[CAPI cackles]
There you are!
[BIGAS]
No chance you're gonna escape!
[IRENE whimpers]
[GERMÁN]
Hm?
Hey, pink shirt!
Why don't you send
that waif our way?
No, I don't think so.
I'm pretty sure she'd
rather stay with me.
Give up the girl
and you can still
walk away clean from all this.
I see. However will we get by?
This guy's just tryin'
to piss us off!
Come on, Donato.
Why don't we slit his
smartass cavalier throat!
I am growing tired of
his chivalrous hero act.
I think you have the
right idea there, Capi.
[GERMÁN]
Mm-hm...
[gasping]
[BIGAS, DONATO, CAPI gasp]
[GERMÁN laughs]
I see now!
Discretion is the
better part of valor!
[BIGAS]
Get back here with that girl!
[CAPI]
You can't outrun us, bastard!
[BIGAS]
We'll get you!
Now, what's your
name, young lady?
It's Irene, my good sir!
Irene, a name fit for an angel.
Tell me, are they behind us?
Not that I can tell.
Aha. But what if they return?
Well, we should hide ourselves.
I know of a place nearby.
[IRENE] We'll be safe here,
I'm positive. No one uses it.
[GERMÁN]
Very sly.
Let's get comfortable while
they tire of the chase.
[IRENE] I can't believe
you'd risk your life
to save a stranger.
[GERMÁN] What can you tell
me about those brigands?
Well, a few nights ago
they were getting rowdy
in a tavern. The big one
tried to grab me,
so I hit him with
a bottle and fled.
They didn't chase after me then,
which I thought was strange,
but when I was walking today,
I ran into them on
the street and, well...
I suppose you had
no bottles on hand.
No. How can I
thank you, good sir?
Worry not.
[IRENE]
Please, I must!
I guess that a kiss
would suffice.
Huh? Uh...
That was quick.
I guess I should have asked
for a greater reward then.
Silly. No one said
that's off the table.
No, no. I wasn't-- Wait, what?
Let's be honest.
You saved my life.
You would be gentle,
wouldn't you?
Uh...
[laughs]
Very well! If you desire,
I, Germán, shall storm
the castle of thy love!
[gasps]
By this heart.
I swear to treat you with
passion and tenderness.
Sir, I...
Be gentle.
Come. Let me lead.
[BIGAS grunts]
[gasps]
[IRENE gasps]
Somebody tell me why the
hell he's naked in here!
Quick! Irene!
We have... to get out
of here right away.
Wait. You seem very calm.
[chuckles] Thanks for
the coinpurse!
No! But...
I was moments away from storming
the castle of thy love!
You mean you really believed
that whole virgin maiden act?
[GERMÁN]
Yeah.
Well, Donato, when you're
right, you are right.
Eh. Anyone with eyes can see
the man's desperate for it.
[GERMÁN] It seems that
I have been beaten.
I will accept my loss.
But, please, if you have any
honor at all, take the money,
yet leave the clothes behind.
[IRENE chuckles]
You just pluck my heartstrings
Ain't no fun to be
had in your version.
[CAPI] Who are you to rob us
of some entertainment, huh?
[sighs] Well, Irene...
Got somethin' to say?
We could've had
something so beautiful.
What?
Enough of that!
Let's cut him to shreds!
Put 'em up, lover boy!
[CAPI, BIGAS growl]
[BIGAS grunts]
Get outta my face!
[IRENE gasps]
[GERMÁN grunts]
[DONATO grunts]
Aw...! New plan!
[gasping]
Stare all you want.
And think of what
could have been.
[gasps]
Son of a bitch!
[GERMÁN pants]
[CAPI]
Get him!
[BIGAS]
Come back here!
[LADY 8A] With all of that
commotion last night,
I couldn't get a wink of sleep.
Did you hear if the
guard caught them yet?
I heard it was a man
and some kind of witch!
Plenty of soldiers out
today, that's for sure.
Who knows what we'll see?
[LADIES]
Huh?
[GERMÁN panting]
[LADIES gasp]
[GERMÁN]
Pardon, ladies!
That'll do!
[LADIES scream]
[SOLDIER 8A]
I heard a shout! What's wrong?
[SOLDIER 8B]
Are you safe?
[LADY 8A]
A man made off with my bonnet!
[LADY 8B] Hardly a man!
More like a three-legged beast!
[SOLDIER 8B] Maybe the one
from last night! After him!
[MAN 8A]
Ah! Get away from me, pervert!
[WOMAN 8A screams] Think of
the children, you heathen!
[GERMÁN]
Bad. Really bad.
I rather stick out like this!
[SOLDIERS yelling]
Great! And now
soldiers. Why not?
[GERMÁN panting]
Good. I think I lost 'em.
Now I just gotta find
something to cover up with.
Any port in a storm.
[GERMÁN]
Yes! This will serve.
[XIMENA]
Hm?
Uh...
[GERMÁN] So sorry, young miss,
but I'm in need of this sheet.
May I borrow it for a time?
[XIMENA]
Mm-hm.
[SOLDIER 8E] There you are!
Quickly! I've found him!
Don't move, or I'll shoot!
[gasps]
[XIMENA gasps]
[GERMÁN grunts]
Dammit, man! Learn how to aim!
[SOLDIER 8F]
Did you kill him?
[SOLDIER 8E]
Uh! No?
[SOLDIER 8G] We need him
alive to tell us where
the witch fled to!
Hold on, what witch?
Quickly, sir. Run!
Much obliged.
[GERMÁN panting]
[GERMÁN]
Ta!
[XIMENA chuckles]
[GERMÁN] I think I
finally lost 'em again.
[BOY 8A]
Who're you?
[BOYS giggling]
Whatcha got for me?
Huh?
Give us something!
Hey, can we have these things?
[GERMÁN]
No! Where are your parents?
--[BOY 8B] Daggers!
--[BOY 8A] Please, Mister!
[GERMÁN] Get off of me,
you little vultures!
Hey, let go!
You can't have those!
Achoo!
Ah...
[SOLDIER 8H]
There he is!
[SOLDIER 8I] The cad! He's
captured a group of children!
[GERMÁN]
I can explain!
[SOLDIER 8H]
Halt, pervert!
[sniffs]
[GERMÁN panting]
[SOLDIER 8H]
Halt!
[SOLDIER 8I]
You degenerate!
This is all a big mistake!
Oh? Do tell.
Like my new bonnet?
[EMA chuckles]
[SOLDIERS yelp]
You have my thanks!
Yeah?
But it seemed like you
were having such fun.
Your definition of fun is
a very broad one, indeed.
My word.
Your son almost dies last
night and I find you naked.
Oh? What happened to him?
He fought the Black Knight.
León was no match
for one such as him.
The Black Knight?
Yes. His name is Bernardo Dion.
[gasps]
I take it you know him?
Where's León?
He managed to escape,
although not by much.
I'd have followed,
but the guard was after me.
[sighs]
What, not rushing to his side?
It's enough that León is alive.
I only hope that he
can take this defeat
as something to learn from.
The day draws near.
I pray my son will discover
what he lacks in time.
It is the sworn duty
of you Makai Knights
to defend and protect.
If the boy only
seeks to gain power
out of his desire for revenge...
He may never be worthy
of the Golden Armor.
[GERMÁN] Thanks for the
rescue. As for him...
I'll do what needs to be done.
You finding pants
is what needs doing.
[GERMÁN]
Quite.
Hello there.
[GERMÁN exhales]
[GARM]
Hm?
[GARM, GERMÁN]
What's the meaning of this?
U-Uh-- Ahem.
Bernardo still lives,
and yet you said nothing.
It wouldn't change your
hunt for Mendooza,
now would it?
I simply neglected to tell
you he was likely to appear.
It seemed rather
irrelevant information.
It's about time I tell you this.
You can sometimes annoy.
[GARM] You wound me,
sweet Zoro. Don't you see?
I kept silent to keep
your pretty mortal heart
from quivering and breaking
at the very thought.
The truth. Is he fallen?
He yet lives, drowned
in the shadows.
I do weep for his loss.
Tch. We are but dogs
for your purpose.
Come, Anna! Keep up with us!
You can shout back
at me all you want,
but it doesn't mean the horse
will suddenly do what I say!
Too bad about Anna.
Her hands spur neither
horses nor men to action.
That's quite uncouth.
No, this is uncouth.
If you catch me, Anna,
you can have me!
God, you're such a letch.
Hyah! Ah! No, wait!
Woah!
[gasps]
Ow. Ow, ow, ow.
Are you all right, Anna?
Uh, yes. Think so.
[GERMÁN]
Truly an astounding dismount.
Thank God you're unharmed.
Or perhaps you just owe it all
to your "natural cushioning"?
[ANNA] Your cushioning's
all in your skull.
[GERMÁN]
Here. Hop up.
[ANNA]
Fine.
Thank you.
[GERMÁN, BERNARDO grunting]
One of these days,
I'd like to take you on
in a true fight!
Just say the word, then.
You know that we can't!
Our code forbids us such duels.
You never were one to
break the rules, were ya?
[BERNARDO]
Hm? I wish that I could.
Huh?
Many's the time my
soul has cried out
for me to spurn
our oath altogether.
In a voice loud as thunder.
Truly?
[BERNARDO grunts]
Well! That was creative.
[BERNARDO] Hmph. That was
a victory, friend.
[GERMÁN]
Victory? Anna!
Can you believe this cheater?
He's still counting it!
Better keep your eye on him!
[ANNA giggles]
[SOLDIER 8L] The witch!
They're fleeing with her!
[SOLDIER 8K]
After them! Quick!
[SOLDIER 8M]
Hurry, men!
[GERMÁN grunts, groans]
Roberto!
[GERMÁN]
Anna! Are you all right?
[ANNA]
Ah. Yes. We are.
[gasps]
[BERNARDO]
Roberto! We must fly!
You're right. Let's go, then.
[gasps]
[GERMÁN] Just a nick.
Here, you should take Anna.
Quickly, now. Both of
you mount up.
I can lead them down
another street.
[GERMÁN]
Are you an idiot?
You know that I'm
the better swords--
Listen to me!
You haven't much chance
with one arm running red!
What're you gonna do?
You damn well can't fight
them all on your own.
I'll find a way.
This, is our only
option, my friend.
[GERMÁN grunts]
You think you can ride?
I think so.
[hooves clacking]
Now go!
Fight well.
We will find you!
Ride hard.
Thank me when next we meet.
[SOLDIERS yelling]
[BERNARDO groaning]
[BERNARDO yells]
[BERNARDO groans]
[BERNARDO]
Forgive me, Roberto.
As of tonight, I wear the
armor of righteousness,
no longer.
[BERNARDO]
Face me, Roberto.
[GERMÁN sneezes]
Bernardo's alive. He'll come.
And I can do naught
but brace myself.
Just my luck.
My clothes are
nowhere to be found.
It's that kinda day.
[GERMÁN grunts]
Oh, now what?
[gasps] Not you again!
Good sir. Thank
heavens it's you!
Huh? You can spare me the tears.
I have nothing else you
can steal. You took it all!
Look, twice in one day
seems a little ambitious.
How about you go ply
your con elsewhere.
[IRENE sobs]
Tell me what happened.
I can't even be sure.
But, well,
after you ran away,
Donato got really angry,
worse than I'd ever seen before!
He attacked us! Please,
please, believe me!
Easy. I know it's true.
[DONATO growling]
[gasps] No. It's Donato!
It'll be all right. Now, Irene.
Please tell me where
I can find my clothes.
Um. A pawn shop.
Aw, dammit!
[DONATO grunts]
[gasps, screams]
No time. Naked it is, then.
[HORROR DONATO growls]
Hey, wait! Stop!
I'm not ready! Not ready!
[HORROR DONATO growls]
[GERMÁN grunts]
You bastard!
I will not lose
in front of a lady!
[HORROR DONATO groans]
[IRENE whimpering]
[GERMÁN] Continue down
this path, and you, too,
will become a monster.
[IRENE whimpers]
Don't you fret.
If you like, I can
stay and keep watch.
You'll be safe with me.
But, I can be
pretty intimidating.
Scarier than any monster.
[IRENE chuckles]
[wolf howls]
[GERMÁN yawns]
[SOLDIER 8N] There he is!
The degenerate's still naked!
You're kidding! Leave me alone!
[XIMENA humming]
[GERMÁN panting]
[SOLDIER 8O]
Halt, man!
[giggles]
[GERMÁN]
León. Good to see you.
Is it really?
Ema told me what happened
during the fight.
That you lost to the
man in the dark armor.
[LEÓN grunts]
It's time to rise
to the challenge.
I can't help you until you do.
I know, thanks.
[GERMÁN]
So what's the plan?
I guess I could use some time.
[GERMÁN]
León, wait.
[GERMÁN] I don't wanna
bore you with details.
Suffice it to say,
I'm naked, and I'm broke.
I'm in a bit of a pickle.
[LEÓN sighs]
[GERMÁN groans]
[GERMÁN]
I'll be waiting, my son.
[GARM]
Hope, it seems, is inherited.
And the lessons instilled
in one's heart.
so fast are sworn into vows.