[BOY A]
Uh.
Mama, look!
Who's that scary man?
[WOMAN gasps]
[STRANGER coughs]
[STRANGER]
Apologies, madam.
I am Doctor Fabian.
Wait... Fabian?
The famous wandering physician?
[FABIAN] I thought I would
give myself over to your care
for a few days.
If you good people could
find it in your hearts
to provide food and lodging, I--
[FABIAN coughing]
I will endeavor to ameliorate
whatever ails you,
free of charge.
So, the tales are true.
[MIKEL]
Mother. Father.
Fortune smiles upon me.
A savior of sorts has come.
I will know what
it is to be a doctor.
At last, I can bid this
hard life a curt farewell.
[MIKEL]
Dr. Fabian?
Do forgive me, my name is Mikel,
I come from the village.
Please allow me to be
your humble apprentice.
I know how to read
and write, sir.
And no task is too menial but
that you may ask me perform it.
--[thud]
--[MIKEL gasps]
Dear god, no.
He-He's corrupted.
[gasps]
[FABIAN gasps]
[MIKEL grunting]
Ahh! Forgive me!
I dare not miss this chance!
[BOOK]
Would you become a doctor?
Take up the book.
Accept my tutelage.
And I will imbue you with skills
outstripping the
royal physicians.
You will become Doctor Fabian.
[MIKEL]
Can this...
Can this be real?
[MIKEL groaning]
[MIKEL screams]
Have mercy. The good
doctor's lodging.
But how in heaven's name?
[XIMENA]
Germán!
I'm headed to the doctor.
If you intend to come
along, you'd best get up.
Did you hear me?
You're making me late! If I have
drag you out of bed myself--
[sighs]
[GERMÁN yelps]
[GERMÁN grunts]
[groaning]
[GERMÁN]
So, Doctor Fabian,
you're somewhat notorious
for never revealing your face.
[MIKEL] And your curiosity
compels you to ask
that I break my iron clad rule.
You're examining mine.
Heh. Figured you might
want to return the favor.
[MIKEL] Mystery is a
potent medicine, good sir.
It is the keystone of my
reputation, my narrative.
People thrill to
contemplate the unseen.
This mask makes the
stories they tell of me
all the more gripping.
Ha! Come.
I'll keep it to myself.
[MIKEL]
There's no injury to the bone.
You ought to heal swiftly.
We're very sorry
to have bothered you.
I didn't know my friend
would be so inquisitive.
[MIKEL]
No bother at all, Miss Ximena.
He's clearly dear to you.
Oh, now I wouldn't say dear.
On your feet, scamp!
We had a late enough
start on the day as it is.
Back to bed if you must.
Okay! Knock it off,
I got the message.
[BOY D gasps]
[BOY D]
It's the naked man!
Ah! If it isn't the
snot-nosed ragamuffin.
Stop that! What's
gotten into you?
Forgive me, he's young.
[GERMÁN]
It's all right, milady.
He's a good lad.
No word of a lie in him.
Hey! You're wearing clothes now.
Indeed I am, and you
sound oddly disappointed.
I take it you've brought
him to see Doctor Fabian.
Yes, I have.
I'm afraid my little boy just
isn't getting any better.
Is it true that masked doctor
will examine him for free?
Absolutely!
Thank heavens that's a relief!
To be honest, I was a
touch reluctant to come.
Oh? Why is that?
Uh, well, to begin with,
I'm frightfully dressed
for the occasion.
You may take it from me, my good
woman, clothes are overrated.
Why, I've stumbled through
town naked as jaybird
without a scratch
on my reputation!
[BOY D laughing]
Yes, so I'm told.
Y'see, our ruler pays
no mind to such trifles.
A most noble fellow indeed.
Much like the good
doctor in here.
You're speaking
of Prince Alfonso?
Soon, this kingdom will be
a land where we all thrive.
Open your heart to the
goodness of the world,
and the blessings flow.
A truly virtuous spirit need
not veil its special radiance.
Likewise, madam, no tailor
can conceal depravity.
--[AMALIA] Germán!
--[LOLA] Mani!
[GERMÁN]
Amalia! Lola!
You pitiless knave!
Where have you been? We
haven't seen you for an age!
No man plays "find the
beauty mark" quite like you.
--[GERMÁN] Uh...
--Huh. Perhaps now
we see the real reason
you shun clothing.
These ladies are just friends.
Uh-huh. Is that why
you look like me
when I get yelled at by
mama for being naughty?
[GERMÁN sighs]
[MIKEL] You see, sir, there
are four humors in the body.
Blood, phlegm, yellow
bile, and black bile.
It's important that we
keep them in balance.
Alas, you have an
overabundance of black bile.
To flush out the excess,
imbibe this medicine with
beans cooked in chicken broth.
Add to that plenty of rest,
then in no time
you'll be right as rain.
I cannot thank you
enough, doctor.
Be well, good sir.
[MIKEL]
Good work, Miss Ximena.
[XIMENA] It's the least
I could do for you.
[MIKEL]
That's all for today, I believe.
But before you go.
Yes, sir?
[MIKEL] Here. To soften
those lovely hands.
[XIMENA] Oh! But we use
so much water at the inn.
My hands will be bone dry again
by tonight. Don't waste it.
[MIKEL] It's for you to
keep, my dear. Please.
Well, in that case...
I accept it gladly, doctor.
[XIMENA'S DAD]
Ximena! I need your help.
[sighs]
Coming.
[MIKEL] Ah, yes,
I've been waiting for you.
How are you feeling
this evening?
[VILLAGER B]
Unimaginably better, thank you.
I feel like I owe you my life.
[MIKEL]
Nonsense.
You healed yourself.
I aided the body's natural
tendency to equilibrium,
nothing more.
In sickness, our inner workings
concoct the most wondrous
medicines all by themselves.
Oh.
[MIKEL]
In fact, at this very moment,
your body possesses a surplus
of such sublime tonics!
[VILLAGER B gasps]
[MIKEL]
In laymen's terms,
at the peak of recovery, the
human body is an apothecary,
producing substances
irresistibly delicious!
[VILLAGER B gasps]
[XIMENA gasps]
Including last night, ten people
have disappeared in two weeks.
Most certainly the
work of a Horror.
This is a map on which the home
of each victim has been marked.
[GERMÁN] Our culprit's hunting
grounds are expansive.
[ALFONSO]
Yes.
In spite of my efforts,
I cannot determine where
the next strike will fall.
I'm inclined to think
the monster itinerant.
Very well, I shall begin
making rounds this evening.
I am in your debt, good uncle.
Ugh! Stop! That obsequious
manner is driving me crazy!
[gasps]
[XIMENA]
That's Prince Alfonso. Why?
Y'see, our ruler pays
no mind to such trifles.
A noble fellow indeed.
Germán... is more than he seems.
[XIMENA]
Excuse me, Señor Germán?
Yes? At your service.
[XIMENA] Well, you see, when
I found you in the street
don't misunderstand I was very
grateful you chose our inn.
I can't quite tell
where this is going.
Ah. Then let me be upfront.
Do you or don't you
have ulterior motives
for lodging here?
That's a loaded question.
I, guess...
Well... Uh... To be
fair, not really?
Sorry! I shouldn't've asked!
Whatever wind brought you here,
thank you for your business.
Up to now, anyway!
[GERMÁN]
Wait! Uh.
What just happened?
[ALFONSO] I apologize for
keeping you waiting, uncle.
[sighs]
[grunts] Uh. You-You look
like you've been to hell.
Think nothing of it, m'boy.
Whatever inferno my
personal life may be,
my duties as a Makai
Knight stand firm.
Let's go.
[MIKEL]
Something troubles you, my dear.
What?
I've not been sleeping
very well of late.
[MIKEL]
Oh?
Insomnia portends
many an illness.
What robs you of your slumber?
I'm afraid I haven't a clue.
[MIKEL] I've no particular
need of you today.
Suppose you go home and
catch up on your rest.
[MIKEL]
Miss Ximena!
Oh, no.
[XIMENA'S DAD]
Damn.
This is intolerable.
Ah. It's you.
Uh, sir, might I ask
where your daughter is.
Poor Ximena's in the
care of Doctor Fabian.
She collapsed unaccountably
just a few days ago.
[MIKEL] Four nights gone
since the malady appeared.
Her fever remains high,
but the boils have subsided.
A hopeful sign.
The symptoms lingering
are treatable.
A combination of ma huang,
licorice, and cinnamon will
hasten her convalescence.
I have outshone my predecessor.
The plague which brought
Doctor Fabian to his knees.
is mine to conquer.
How rich and succulent
her flavor will be
as she wards off this
pestilence. I cannot wait!
[GERMÁN]
Doctor! How is she?!
[MIKEL]
Better than you suppose.
[GERMÁN]
Ximena.
Germán.
Come, be strong.
You will beat this.
[MIKEL]
She's fine.
By nightfall, she'll be
able to take solid food.
[GERMÁN]
That's good.
[MIKEL] I'll be moving on once
she's made a full recovery.
I admire your efforts on behalf
of the townsfolk, doctor.
You're a true Samaritan.
[MIKEL]
I'm pleased to be of service.
Alas, as sickness admits of
no border, I must be itinerant.
[grunts]
[MIKEL]
Señor Germán?
Uh, I... must be going myself.
I thank you for
taking care of her.
Clearly, she is in gifted hands.
[MIKEL laughing]
[MIKEL]
Exactly as I predicted.
I will take my time savoring
this triumphant body.
An ultimate reward for
the ultimate physician.
[GERMÁN] Your prey never
brought you off the beaten path.
[MIKEL yelps]
They flocked to you from
every corner of the realm,
did they not, Doctor?
[MIKEL]
A Makai Knight?
You devoured your patients
like a wolf in winter.
[MIKEL]
That's not true.
I didn't devour all of them.
I eat only one human
being per day.
To permit binging is to court
distemper of the humors!
[MIKEL] I've treated far more
than I've treated myself to.
Let me assure you, sir,
The number of lives I've ended
are nothing compared
to the ones I've saved.
Would you destroy me?.
I'll wager that you've
saved fewer than you think.
The human will to survive is
much stronger than you realize.
We rise above and
carry on, come what may.
That will is what a Makai
Knight is sworn to defend!
[MIKEL]
I see.
If only there were a cure for
such stubborn pig-headedness!
[GERMÁN grunts]
[MIKEL groans]
[gasps]
[GERMÁN]
What is that?!
[MIKEL] Nothing less than
the glorious culmination
of my acumen as a
healer, foolish knight!
I'm a genius, you see!
A practitioner of my
art like none other.
[MIKEL]  My strength waxes.
My power overflows!
[GERMÁN grunts]
[GERMÁN yells]
[MIKEL roars]
[MIKEL]
Ah.
Lacerations on head,
left antebrachial region
and right brachial region.
Compound fracture of
the right femoral bone.
Slight damage of
the internal organs.
[MIKEL groaning]
[MIKEL]
I must treat you!
What?
[MIKEL] Damn it! The urge
to heal is too strong!
Stay away from me! No!
What the hell are you doing?!
[MIKEL]
Calm yourself.
You'll be right
as rain in no time.
[GERMÁN groaning]
[GERMÁN]
Ow, ow, ow, ow, ow, ow!
[MIKEL] This is much too
potent for a normal person.
But for a Makai Knight?
[GERMÁN groaning]
Seriously?
I feel like a powerhouse!
[MIKEL]
No infirmity is beyond my skill.
Let us test it further.
You'll probably regret that.
[GERMÁN yelling]
[MIKEL]
No! No, how dare you?!
Bastard.
Germán.
Ximena. You-You've awakened.
Seems I have. How
observant of you.
'S good to see you well.
You caught a touch
of the plague.
Oh, dear.
Father's had to manage alone.
Don't give it a thought.
Doctor's orders are
uninterrupted rest.
You mustn't let the pestilence
get a foothold again, my dear.
[gasps]
I mean, my friend!
Germán, I saw you meeting
with His Highness the Prince.
I can't imagine what brings
an aristocrat like you here,
but it's none of my affair.
Wait... I'm an aristocrat now?
You must be.
What other reason
would a prince have
for paying deference to you?
You're a very silly woman.
I resent that. I saw it.
Do not mock me.
Let's mull it over
carefully for a moment.
Can someone as
unsophisticated as me
be so high born as all that?
Now, I shan't deny
what you witnessed,
but your interpretation's
a bit romantic.
[XIMENA]
Oh, is it?
I'll explain some other time.
So, you don't consider this
place beneath you? Really?
I don't stay where
I don't feel at home.
[XIMENA] Please, if you felt at
home you wouldn't be so polite.
Ugh. There's no
winning with you.
Is it my peasant hands
that repulse you?
Or my clothes?
Uh. What are you
babbling about, Ximena?!
Your hands are adorable
And your clothes.
Ugh! Now you're
teasing me, ogre.
Ogre? Your fire's back
at full bore again, eh?
Would you please shut up?
I must give thanks
to Doctor Fabian.
Imagine if he hadn't
come to our town.
Indeed.
Alas, I'm afraid the good
doctor had to be on his way.
He asked for me offer you
a farewell in his stead.
So it goes.
He follows his calling.
There are many people out there
yet to benefit from his help.
Oh. What a strange little bird!
Hello there!
Aw. I guess no one stays.
[GERMÁN]
Hmm.
[XIMENA]
Germán?
Your face is enviable.
What?
I, uh... I should like to see
it around for a good while yet.
You know, the things you say
leave me feeling
quite perplexed.
[XIMENA]
What does that mean?
[GERMÁN] Nevertheless, if the
lady wishes to behold my face,
let her sleep content to
see it when she awakens.
I take special pride in
this illustrious beard.
[chuckles] Yes, you do.
Now. Trade the
chit-chat for rest.
Germán?
[GERMÁN]
Hm?
Thank you very much.
[GERMÁN]
Of course.
It is exceedingly rare
for you to call upon me.
Rest assured I did
not summon you here
for the pleasure
of your company.
State your business
and be done with it.
I'd much prefer to
be in a warm bath.
Very well. Until further notice,
you and Mendoza will
be partners in the field.
What? Surely you're joking.
[knocking]
[XIMENA]
Germán?
[door closes]
Where'd you go?
[GARM]
The quiet dark of night.
The heavens bestow
a delicate, white gift.
Why must the snowfall
be so fleeting?