[LARA] Where are you
headed after you leave us?
If I were you, I'd go
somewhere nice and warm.
[MOTHER] Your hard work
made all of this possible!
[LARA]
If you had a mind to,
you'd be welcome to stay
with us indefinitely.
[GRANDPA]
Good work.
[LARA] Something tells
me Abuela's right.
Next year's going to
be a good harvest.
[LEÓN]
Here, let me.
[LARA]
Thank you.
[LEÓN]
Something wrong?
No it... it's just not that
long ago I had to help you.
Doesn't seem fair.
[LEÓN chuckles]
You prefer me lazy?
[LARA laughs]
Oh, look.
They used to call this place
the old fairy mound. Neat, huh?
Stories about it
go way, way back.
The fairies were said to
hold grand banquets here
once upon a time,
supposedly every night.
If you were traveling after dark
and some awful creature chased
you, you could hide here.
Comforting, right?
But like I said,
the stories are old.
The Watchdog Center.
[LEÓN] This is an entrance.
No mistake, it must be.
How long has this
place been in ruins?
Still an effective barrier
against Horrors though. Huh.
[LARA]
León, hello?
What's gotten into you?
You do realize that there's
no such things as fairies?
Yeah, 'course.
Even if there were, this
village would hardly need 'em.
[LEÓN] It's obsolete.
All but forgotten.
A lot like... me.
[LEÓN]
Let's go home, shall we?
[LARA] That look.
I've never seen it before.
[LARA]
We're home!
You two took your time.
How anyone can be so leisurely
gathering wood, I'll never know.
[GRANDMA] The prince himself
has come, young lady.
He's visiting his lordship at
the manor house as we speak.
Isn't that exciting?
[LORD]
As you see, Your Highness,
the land is rich in
beauty, but little else.
What we posses in quietude,
we lack in arable soil.
Do not underestimate
your treasure.
Peace is a thing to take
pride in, your lordship.
To have it as a neighbor
is a blessing.
Indeed, I am inspired.
[LORD]
We are not worthy, Your Grace.
The people will
thrill to see you.
How fares the city
of Santa Bard?
I trust the rebuilding
is near completion.
Yes.
That being said, one does
still hear of demons.
A handful are wreaking havoc
where there is quarter.
The wind of rumor reaches far.
A shame about Valdona
of Romero and Orvien.
Fortunately, rumor is
all that reaches us.
The demons keep their distance.
That is good to hear.
[VILLAGERS chatting]
[ALFONSO chuckles]
[DOG barking]
Uh! León.
[ALFONSO] I knew in
my heart you'd survived.
[LEÓN]
Yes.
I am glad to find
you in good health.
Uncle says precious
little on the subject,
but I know he's been worried.
[LEÓN]
I'm sure he has been.
Forgive me. Words fail--
[LEÓN]
Alfonso.
I understand the
weight of what I did.
And I know that
my agonizing over it
doesn't change a damn thing.
[LEÓN]
Little though it's worth,
for my crimes against
Valiante, I am deeply sorry.
I have done an evil thing.
I no longer have the right
to be a Makai Knight.
Wisdom often comes too late.
Only now do I understand
what my father meant.
What it is that compels men
of the armor to act as they do.
Why they fight.
Why they protect.
I was unfit to wield a sword
because I couldn't see
past my own hatred.
All of that feels like
another life to me now.
Yet I remember when
our paths first crossed
as though it were yesterday.
[ALFONSO]
I as well. Orvien.
I'm ashamed to say it,
but at the time I thought you
no more than a naïve squire.
[chuckles] Yes, well,
hardly an unfair assessment.
[LEÓN]
No. The real naïve one was me.
Without question.
So, were you as shocked as me?
Who'd have ever guessed he
knew such highborn people?
He comes from a
different world than us.
If I was him, I'd
pro'bly wanna go back.
Sooner or later, anyway.
It's bound to be warmer there.
[LEÓN] I didn't know what
it was to live under one roof.
We always just kept moving.
Home for me was a campfire
and the open road.
I thought I was worldly,
thought I had some experience.
But for all my travels,
I might as well have stayed
in my mother's belly.
All I cared for was revenge.
All I saw was fire.
It consumed me,
blinded me to the world.
Like I said, wisdom
often comes late.
León,
I used to wonder if I would've
handled things differently.
Were I in your shoes,
I'm not certain I could've
fulfilled my duties either.
Had it been my mother.
In truth, only the slightest
twist of fate separates us.
My condolences. I heard
about the queen.
When all's said and done,
'tis impossible to know
another man's mind.
People cannot know,
unless they have actually
experienced something
for themselves.
[LEÓN]
I agree.
Nicely said, and exactly why
they need your protection.
May I be the last
to bear such sorrow.
No one should ever have
to suffer like that again.
[ALFONSO]
I take pride in being chosen.
I will live up to
the honor as best I can,
doing right by the
armor at every turn.
Thinking always of you.
Yes, well, it's an honor
you were born for, cousin.
[ALFONSO]
León!
If I speak out of turn,
forgive me, but... you seem...
...you seem to have found
something you wish to protect.
[LEÓN]
That may be.
[LARA]
Uh.
[LEÓN]
Sorry to keep you waiting.
Let's go.
Oh. I thought...
[LEÓN] We were just
having a little talk.
Catching up, so to speak.
Don't act like
you're not leaving.
[LEÓN]
What?
[LARA] A man who
"catches up" with princes
isn't the kind of man who
settles in a place like this.
[LEÓN]
Think again.
I'm not going anywhere.
'Less, you're tired of me?
[LARA]
Mh-mh.
[LARA chuckles]
[LARA]
Race you home!
We'd best hurry. It'll be
dark 'fore you know it!
[LEÓN]
Whoa!
--[LARA] C'mon, find your feet!
--[LEÓN] Give me a chance!
[ALFONSO]
I'm not certain.
All signs point to it
being the work of a Horror.
Evidence suggests
that multiple victims
have already fallen prey.
So, you didn't just
come here to see me.
No, I am on the hunt.
And though I will not rest
till the beast is felled.
In the meantime, take care.
[LEÓN]
A Horror? In this village?
[SOLDIER A shivers]
[SOLDIER A]
Bitter cold day, isn't it?
[SOLDIER B] It'll probably
snow ere the sun sets.
Why're we standing on such
a godforsaken patch of clay?
What could His
Highness be up to?
Who could tell
except the prince.
Rest assured, his whims
are beyond the reach
of our understanding.
Zaruba, what say you?
Be vigilant.
This one may well be the most
formidable you've faced yet.
A Grand Magus. The Horror
that burrows underfoot.
[gasps]
[GRANDPA]
Lara.
Sorry!
I'm coming! I'm coming!
We keep this up, we'll
be finished by nightfall.
Excellent. We must do our
best to safeguard this lot.
These seeds are our livelihood.
If all goes well and they sprout
next year, well, never you mind.
We can pay back our debt?
Children ought not be
concerned with such things.
Life's too short.
I'm not a child anymore, Abuelo.
[LARA]
León! Need help?!
You shouldn't be up here.
Don't be silly.
I know what I'm doing. Guess who
tended the roof before you.
That's it for this part.
I didn't climb up here
to be treated like a baby.
Give me a job to do.
Whoa.
[LARA grunts]
[LEÓN]
Isn't that lovely?
[LARA]
You think so?
There's not much to see.
You said so yourself, actually.
[LEÓN]
I did?
[LARA]
Yep.
I was wrong.
Knowing you has made all
the difference in how I see.
You've really opened up my eyes.
Don't talk like
that. It's weird.
[LARA]
Uh.
[MOTHER] Would you look
at that, it's snowing!
[GRANDMA] Lara! Come down
and give your Abuela a hand!
[LEÓN gasps]
[LEÓN]
Am I imagining things?
[screaming]
Let's go inside.
It's too cold out here.
[LEÓN grunts]
[HORROR growling]
[DOG whining]
[LEÓN grunts]
[door opens]
[LARA]
What's going on? What happened?!
Stop! Don't come out!
Stay in the house!
[LARA]
What?!
Uh!
What is that?!
[LEÓN]
Run! Find somewhere to hide!
[LEÓN grunts]
[LEÓN yelling]
[BOTH yelping]
[LARA]
León, what was that thing?!
[LEÓN] Get out of here!
As fast as you can!
[GRANDMA] But surely that
thing's dead, isn't it?
A Horror won't die
from a wound like that.
Only a Makai Knight
can defeat it.
So you have to leave!
Right now! Get to
the fairy mound!
You'll be safe.
It's a kind of barrier
against monsters like these.
[GRANDPA] We can't just
leave our seeds behind.
You have no choice. Now go!
Young man, those seeds
are everything to us.
Damn you, this family
depends on their yield.
If we leave them behind,
we'll have nothing,
do you understand?
Nothing!
Listen, I'm sorry.
There's no time!
You must get Lara and
the others to safety!
[GRANDPA grunting]
[LARA]
Abuelo, please! He's right!
[GRANDPA sighs]
[ALFONSO]
León.
You seem to have found
something you wish to protect.
[LEÓN]
I can't protect anything.
Not as I am now.
Hurry, León.
[MOTHER]
God have mercy!
What?
[MOTHER]
Look!
[gasps] Our house in on fire!
Why in heaven's name
is this happening?!
No! I'm going back;
we can't let the seeds burn!
Abuelo! Abuelo, wait!
[LEÓN]
Lara, please make it in time.
[LEÓN grunting]
[ALFONSO]
León!
Tell me where the Horror struck!
[ALFONSO] Talk to me.
Get ahold of yourself!
[LEÓN]
I-It's at the farmhouse.
I can't do anything.
I'm useless!
Leave the fighting to me.
You get to safety.
Don't let it kill
my family, Alfonso!
Protect Lara! Please!
[ALFONSO gasps]
[ALFONSO]
León...
I beg of you!
You needn't beg.
The Horror is as good as dead!
[LEÓN]
I'll see to it...
...Lara gets to the mound.
[HORROR crunching]
[ALFONSO]
Foul beast.
How many lives have you
blindly gorged yourself on?!
[LEÓN]
Please let them be there.
This should be
the swiftest path.
Why are you here?
Uh!
[ALFONSO grunting]
[HORROR roaring]
[ALFONSO yelling]
[ALFONSO]
No you don't!
[LEÓN crying]
[groaning]
[LARA]
León.
--[LARA] León.
--Lara.
[LARA]
Is that you?
I can't see.
[LEÓN]
Lara?
[LEÓN gasps]
[LEÓN]
Lara!
[HORROR growling]
[ALFONSO yelling]
[LEÓN]
Talk to me.
Say something.
There you are.
Lara!
We shouldn't have come back.
We should've listened to you.
But those seeds were everything.
I'm so sorry.
It's all right. Don't apologize.
You're going to be...
going to be fine.
[LARA]
You're leaving. I know you are.
[LEÓN]
Lara, I already told you.
This is home now.
I'm not going anywhere.
Whatever happens, you and me.
[LARA]
Don't be silly.
You have a whole other
life, far from here.
[LEÓN]
Lara...
Goodbye, Traveler.
It was nice having you.
I wish you could stay here.
Maybe next time,
take me with you.
[LEÓN crying]
[GARM] His only wish was to
protect that precious smile.
Yet again, he takes
up the blade,
consumed by the fires of hatred.