[ALFONSO]
Upon my sword I vow.
We will rid our
fair country of Mendoza.
Come. Let us so swear.
[LEÓN] If they're holding
the queen inside the castle,
do you know where she'd be?
[ALFONSO]
I want my mother freed,
but I returned
to save Valiante.
My land must come first.
[MENDOZA] A moon in crimson,
as if soaked in blood.
It heralds the beast
that shall lead this world
to the purifying flame.
Even the strength of
your mighty Watchdog Council
is as nothing.
All will flee before it!
[LEÓN grunts]
[ALFONSO yells]
The summoning of the
Blood Moon is almost complete,
you uncouth children.
It's too late.
[LEÓN growls]
[ALFONSO] León!
Don't worry about Mendoza!
We have a bigger target!
[HORROR 11A growls]
The witch's progeny.
Born amidst the screams
of your immolated mother.
What a pleasure
to meet you at last.
[LEÓN grunts]
You murdered her,
you monster!
Careful, boy.
Drawing strength
from a personal vendetta
does not become
a knight, you know.
[LEÓN yells]
[LEÓN grunts]
You burn as well.
[ALFONSO grunts]
León!
[LEÓN]
What the--?
[ALFONSO]
León?
[LEÓN grunts]
[LEÓN gasps]
Mother?
[HORROR 11A growls]
[ALFONSO]
Cousin!
[MENDOZA] You don't
remember her death.
How could you?
You were but seconds old.
So I'll show you.
Observe as your
dear mother is consumed,
as the very flesh
which housed your body
burns away and her bones
crack and blacken.
[LEÓN]
Don't do this.
[MENDOZA] I imagine
your father told you
her suffering was
the thing of a moment.
Sadly, nothing could
be more false.
[ANNA]
I'm burning! I'm burning!
Oh, God. Somebody save me!
Please, I'll do anything!
I don't wanna die like this!
[LEÓN]
No!
[ALFONSO] Don't believe
Mendoza's lies!
He's hitting you
where he knows you to be
most wounded and vulnerable!
[LEÓN breathes shakingly]
No, child of the witch.
I deliver you naught
but the truth. See?
Though she's hardly
recognizable now,
watch carefully your
mother's fiery demise.
[MALE SUBJECT 1E]
Death to the witch!
[MALE SUBJECT 1F]
Burn for all eternity!
[FEMALE SUBJECT 1C] This is for
my daughter, you monster!
[LEÓN yelling]
[screams]
[HORROR 11A growls]
[ALFONSO] León! Cousin!
Snap out of it!
[ANNA]
León. My darling baby.
[LEÓN gasps]
[ZARUBA inhales]
[GERMÁN]
Mm. Damn it!
Don't you dare succumb. León!
[ALFONSO grunting]
[LEÓN growls]
[ALFONSO]
Impossible!
[MENDOZA]
A thing of beauty.
[ALFONSO]
What have you done?
I just lit the kindling.
What you see now
is the true form
of the Golden Armor,
replete with hatred.
It's a testament to the
worst in the human heart.
[ALFONSO]
Mendoza! You bastard!
[HORROR 11A growling]
--[LEÓN grunting]
--[HORROR 11A groaning]
[ALFONSO] How? How can
this gold-plated beast
be the Garo of before?
[LEÓN growling]
[ALFONSO] Oh, no!
He's heading into town!
León! Wait!
[MENDOZA] It would seem
the Makai Knights
aren't what they used to be.
A pity, but our plans will
see fruition all the sooner.
Very soon.
[LEÓN roars]
[CROWD screaming]
[ALFONSO]
Snap out of it, León!
The capital
will not survive this!
Aah!
[breathing deeply]
[CROWD screaming]
Here! These will
protect you a bit!
[grunting]
Hurry, everyone!
This devil's the
legendary Knight of Light?
Valiante's savior?
[LEÓN roars]
[ALFONSO] This night,
he'll be the death of us all!
[ALFONSO] He gives free reign
to his lust for vengeance.
How easily he abandons
his duty to the people
he's sworn to protect!
León! With my sword
in hand, I defy you!
Come what may!
Uncle, forgive what
I am to do!
Your son is mad with rage!
Do not try to stop me.
[GERMÁN]
The emblem at his waist.
[ALFONSO gasps]
Hit the Makai emblem.
That should dispel
the Golden Armor.
Strike with all your might.
You have to hit hard enough
to run him through.
It should be me.
It's a father's duty
to discipline his son.
Uh! Were it not
for this shoulder,
I'd kill him myself.
Do it. Please.
While he still has
a soul left to redeem.
Yes, Uncle.
León, how could you
be so numb?
Even to the words
of your own father.
[LEÓN gasps]
Mother!
[crying]
[screams]
León, that's enough!
[LEÓN growls]
[MENDOZA] If all Makai Knights
and Alchemists were as foolish
as this pair, I would have
been content to let nature
take its course and have them
kill each other off.
[ALFONSO grunts]
[LEÓN roars]
[GERMÁN gasps]
[ALFONSO]
Santa Bard!
[grunts]
[ALFONSO] I will save you!
Capital and kingdom alike!
I will preserve them both!
[ALFONSO]
Stand down, León!
Heap no more sins
atop your head!
[LEÓN growls]
[ALFONSO grunts]
Just look at what
you've become, chico!
I preferred the old you!
[ALFONSO]
Miss Ema!
[LEÓN roars]
[ALFONSO yells]
[ALFONSO grunts]
[LEÓN roars]
[ALFONSO yells]
[ALFONSO grunts]
My son.
[gasps]
León!
[GERMÁN] Forgive me.
You always burned.
But I never knew a way
to put the flames out.
[yells]
[LEÓN]
Blaaahhh!
[LEÓN grunts]
[LEÓN laughs]
[groans]
[GERMÁN]
Anna. I am sorry.
Germán!
Get up off your ass!
León!
[GERMÁN grunts]
[gasps, exhales]
[GERMÁN]
You held back, Alfonso?
I attacked with every
bit of strength I had.
[HORROR 11A growls]
Better late than never.
[HORROR 11A growls lowly]
Good uncle, the blood
of the Golden Knight Garo
flows through my veins,
as well as León's.
[gasps]
That I may protect
the people of Valiante!
O Father. Mother mine.
Be with me in this dark hour!
[ALFONSO grunts]
How many Golden Knights
is it now?
Their tenure's so short,
it's hard to keep count.
[ALFONSO] Know that
I will be the last!
[LEÓN groans softly]
[ALFONSO yells]
You're right about
being the last one.
And now, you will languish
in the belly of that beast
as it wanders Makai
for all eternity.
My goodness.
How soon they grow up.
To think that I once
held you in my arms
when you were but a babe.
[HORROR 11A groans]
[LEÓN groans]
My armor.
Give it back to me.
Son, that armor is not
yours to take back.
Not anymore.
Alfonso is its new
lord and master.
What became of Mendoza?
He's dead, León.
No doubt about it.
So... I was useless?
[LEÓN]
Give it back. Please.
Give me back the armor!
Garo belongs to me!
Give it back!
[ALFONSO]
You want it back,
while the city of
our birth lies in flames?
Look around!
Mendoza didn't do this with
the Horrors at his command.
It was you!
[LEÓN gasps]
Santa Bard suffers
because of you!
I'm to believe that you can
be trusted as a Makai Knight
to safeguard the lives
of the innocent?
[LEÓN] My mother.
It's all I have of her!
[GERMÁN]
God damn it!
That is enough!
Don't you get it, León?
You're a member of the
Makai Knights no longer!
You need to accept that!
[gasps]
Think about this moment.
How it came to this.
And what's next for you.
Figure yourself out,
or you'll spend the rest
of your life on your knees!
If you want it, you'll
have to take it by force.
[ALFONSO] You lack the
courage for even that?
I'm disappointed
sin you, cousin.
[sighs]
What now?
A boy cannot
truly become a man
until you let him fall,
and stand up on his own.
Spoken like a man.
[sighs]
You damn Makai Knights
sure are something else.
[chuckles]
Thanks for the help. Really.
[GERMÁN]
Stand up, León.
[XIMENA] Thank goodness.
The fires have burned out!
You see?
The worst of it's over.
[MALE SERVANT 12A]
The Prince!
[FEMALE SERVANT 12A]
Master Alfonso!
I am relieved
to see you all well.
[MALE SERVANT 12B] Praise God
you're safe, Highness!
What of my
father and mother?
Though the King's malady
still leaves him bedridden,
he came to no further harm.
The Queen was not so fortunate.
[door creaks, clangs]
Mother.
Oh, Mother.
[ALFONSO]
Why, Mother? Why this?
Didn't you know that I was
coming back to save you?
[LAURA] She told me her deepest
fear was that Mendoza
would use her
as leverage against you.
When she heard that
you'd returned to Santa Bard,
she dismissed all the servants.
[gasps]
And took her own life.
[sobbing]
Dearest Mother,
I swore I would return here
and set you free.
And now I discover that
your most noble of souls
has gone on to its reward.
Please, God!
Please, let her know
peace at last.
[sobbing]
[LEÓN]
What do I do from now on?
I don't know.
I have nothing left.
No armor. No calling.
Mendoza is dead.
So, there's no reason
for me to fight anymore.
[XIMENA grunting]
--[distant crash]
--[XIMENA gasps]
[XIMENA] Good sir!
Are you all right? Hey!
[GERMÁN groans]
[ALFONSO] Oh, Mother.
You laid down your sweet life
that Mendoza would
have no sway over me.
León. I chastised you
for your loss of control,
but had it been my mother...
...I daresay I would have
lashed out as well.
[birds cawing]
[GARM] With the dawn,
you awaken to find that
who you are no longer matters.
Of what use are you if you
cannot wield a sword?