[VILLAGERS screaming]
[yelling]
[GERMÁN]
Garo chose you.
I suggest you take
pride in that.
[ALFONSO] I make this pledge
to you here and now!
Valiante will again
see the light!
[VILLAGERS]
Salve! Salve, Valiante!
Salve! Salve, Prince Alf--!
[JULIO] When I inherited
this place from the boss,
people were really supportive.
"You'll do Jordi proud," they
said. "Give it your best."
Of course, to be honest,
even with all the encouragement,
I didn't exactly feel confident.
Oh, you can hear me, right?
Great. Visual good? 'Kay.
At the moment, we're
in the weapons store
of Jordi's old workshop.
My name is Julio.
These guys? Only the most
skilled trades-people in town!
All gathered here to marshal
their talents toward one goal.
What might that
goal be, you ask?
Nothing less than creating
the kingdom's Legendary
Knight of Light!
Do you love it?
Consider it our gift
to Santa Bard.
[JULIO] The great fire that
nearly reduced our town to ashes
wasn't some natural disaster.
But the work of a giant,
diabolical monster.
When all seemed lost,
out of nowhere appeared a hero
who cut the infernal beast
down in one fell swoop.
It's was incredible!
Legend calls him
the Knight of Light.
"Like a wolf forged of gold,
impervious to flame."
That's how eyewitnesses
described him, anyway.
Talk about a beacon of hope.
And this is where we come in.
Amazing as the
Knight of Light is,
he can't be everywhere at once.
So, we're crafting a duplicate.
Now, granted from a
logical perspective
the whole idea seems
reasonably impossible.
And it is, if I'd tried
to do by myself.
Luckily, though, I cast
my net pretty wide.
Ha! Forge one with our
own hands, you say?
There's a capital idea.
Yes! He'll gleam like Phoebus!
The pinnacle of
our craftsmanship!
It will be splendid!
Trust me, Julio,
that sort of strength
only comes at great
personal cost.
A man's heart can only bear
so much enforced solitude.
Señor Pancho, I'm not
exactly sure what you mean,
but be careful.
A worthy enterprise, indeed,
or I don't know the
meaning of the word.
To protect our neighbors
through craftsmanship,
I am thrilled to take part.
Yes, indeed! What are
we waiting for?
Let's pool our talents
and get it done.
[JULIO] And so, with the best
and brightest under one roof,
the time has finally come,
to bring it to life.
[RAFAEL] Where the
human heart embraces evil,
Horrors feast, possessing
those who invite them.
Such vile, poisonous
creatures have been hunted
since time out of mind.
Relentlessly pursued by Men of
the Armor: The Makai Knights!
[PANCHO] No, no. The
original didn't have those.
Certainly not there.
[MANUEL]
I'm telling you he did!
I saw it with my own two eyes!
[PETRONA]
Well, either way,
one thing I'm certain
he had was a scarf.
Some shade of red,
if memory serves.
[BRUNO]
Wait, what about his sword?
Idiots. If I didn't know better,
I'd think you'd never
laid eyes on the man.
You're describing a
nobleman on holiday.
His eyes burned like
the embers of a furnace,
of that much I'm sure.
One arm was longer
than the other.
Yes, possibly retractable.
What if we gave him wings?
Do you think we
could make him fly?
Correct me if I'm wrong,
but I believe he could
open his mouth to bellow.
There can be no argument;
his armor glowed like the sun.
He resembled a wolf all aflame.
So lovely! Whatever else we
do about his appearance,
we mustn't overlook
that dazzling sheen!
[MANUEL]
Right. Agreed.
Oh, and, Julio, about the head.
Do your damnedest to
make it awe-inspiring.
[JULIO]
Um...
Let's just be sure we're
consulting the drawings, okay?
All the parts have to fit.
[ALL gasping]
[EMERICO]
Well, seems only fair
we should let the
boy hop in first.
[JULIO]
Oh, that's nice of you,
but you all will be the
ones wearing it, not me.
[PANCHO]
Ah, good point.
Didn't think of that.
I'm the burliest here,
so it makes sense for me
to have a go, I s'pose.
[MANUEL]
No offense, Pancho, but, uh,
it seems like it'd be a bit
of a snug fit for you.
Hell, Petrona has to make
half your wardrobe.
Uh. Perhaps it oughta
be me. I'm trim.
[EMERICO]
Oh-ho! And fit as a fiddle!
Excellent idea! I second Bruno!
[EMERICO]
Perfect!
[JULIO]
Okay, try moving around.
[BRUNO]
It's too heavy.
I can't so much as wiggle a toe.
Aw, now what? The armor
looks so spectacular!
Please tell me this doesn't mean
we have to start back
at square one.
What if we made it
self-propulsive, you know,
something like a
clockwork doll, maybe?
[EMERICO]
Hmm.
That might be
beyond our abilities.
Besides, it's not a toy!
[JULIO]
Actually, give me a night.
I think Señora Petrona might
really be on to something.
With these modifications,
Señor Bruno should be
able to maneuver it.
[PANCHO]
Hold on a moment there, lad.
Wouldn't these make
the outfit even heavier?
No! Just the opposite!
Julio, these modifications
just might be a game-changer.
'N fact, you may have stumbled
on the invention of the century!
Oh, this gets my
gears a-turnin'!
Indeed. This is brilliant.
I say we enlist Camillo
from the bath house.
[BRUNO] Yes, yes. I know it's
intricate and time consuming,
but you owe me. Just
follow these schematics.
The sooner you start,
the sooner you can be done.
[EMERICO]
Julio? Believe I'll call it day.
See you bright
and early tomorrow.
[EMERICO]
Jordi, I hope you can see this.
The apprentice appears
to be surpassing the master.
[EMERICO] I guess the apple
doesn't fall far from the tree.
[BRUNO]
Sorry for the wait.
Behold!
Yes. The fruits of Camillo's
intense all-nighter.
[JULIO]
Wow!
Señor Camillo's outdone
himself! This is amazing!
[EMERICO] Indeed, so why isn't
the man here to unveil it?
Ah. The poor devil
worked himself sick.
He's laid up now. Got
a touch of the fever.
Not a dull fellow, but
not exactly acclimated
to mental acrobatics
of this caliber.
Well, when he's done
being an invalid,
we'll have to
thank him properly.
Ha! Just look at it!
Now all we have to do is attach
it and we're ready to go.
[metal clinking]
[EMERICO]
All right!
Think it's ready?
[PETRONA] Let me just
come right out and say it.
I think we've gone a tiny bit
afield of our original design.
[MANUEL] Bah! We'll slap
some gold paint on it later.
It'll look great!
Well? Let's do it! Hop in
and give the ol' guy a spin!
Very well, then.
[ALL gasping]
[BRUNO groaning]
[BRUNO coughing]
Good heavens, what a fright.
My life flashed before my eyes.
[PANCHO]
Figures.
[ALL]
Huh?
[PANCHO] You can't very well
expect the blasted thing to work
if you don't let me have a say.
[JULIO]
Well, Señor Pancho.
Uhh. What is that?
[PANCHO]
Well, it ain't Sunday dinner.
This is no normal cut of meat.
See, a thought occurred to me
when I was lookin'
over your plans.
Metal pipes around
the waist are too rigid.
Their joints aren't articulated
enough to keep from snapping
under the strain
when the suit moves.
Oh! I follow you! Why,
Pancho, that's ingenious!
I'm embarrassed to say
I don't quite understand.
What's being proposed?
That's it! Of course!
The pipes connecting
the engine to the limbs
aren't flexible enough.
They either restrict our
movement or bust altogether.
But, if we used
another material--
[EMERICO]
Yes! Absolutely right!
If you want durability
and flexibility,
this stuff's precisely what you
need. Mother Nature's piping.
Surely he's not suggesting
what I think he is?
Using intestines
instead of pipe? Yes!
You'll need several layers
to withstand the pressure,
and it just so happens I have
some to spare right here.
We'd be fools not to use it.
[ALL]
Ugh.
Oh.
It--
Will be very
heartwarming to know...
...that my dear son lives on.
Your son?
No, no!
By son, I mean my
prized livestock.
Sebastian was such a good boy.
[ALL grunting]
[PANCHO]
Well? What do you say?
Shall we finish what we started?
[PANCHO]
Beautiful.
[MANUEL]
All right, Bruno. Get inside.
[BRUNO] To be perfectly frank,
I have some trepidation.
[EMERICO]
Aw, c'mon!
Have confidence!
Trust in your cohorts!
[JULIO]
You can do this.
The boss would laugh
in the face of fear.
He'd laugh at you right
about now, actually.
[BRUNO]
Hm. Good point.
I couldn't bear the thought
of his laughing at my expense.
[BRUNO]
Let's do this!
[ALL gasping]
Whoa, careful. Move slow.
Easy does it, Señor Bruno.
[BRUNO]
Indeed.
[JULIO] Wow. I wish you
could see this, boss.
These people are
absolutely amazing.
Stubborn, sure.
And surly. But amazing.
Truth be told,
they're the most dependable
bunch I could ever ask for.
[laughing]
[CROWD chattering]
[BRUNO] Not to pat ourselves
on the back, but...
...I'd say we have a winner.
True. We've cobbled together
a magnificent piece
of machinery, my friend.
Personally, I couldn't
be more proud. Ha.
[PETRONA]
Gentle townsfolk!
We give you:
The Knight of Light!
Bring your wrongs down to
Old Master Jordi's smithy
and see them put
to rights in a flash!
[ALFONSO]
Mmm.
Please, uncle, you're
more than welcome
to use to front entrance
just like everyone else.
[GERMÁN laughs]
I know, but this method
keeps me on my toes.
[ALFONSO] The Lord Chamberlain
brings me interesting news.
Apparently, someone's been
seen gallivanting about
in a suit of golden armor.
Yes. I've heard. No need to
trouble yourself, my boy.
Uncle! The fool could
endanger himself!
[GERMÁN]
It's probably some blacksmith
trying to drum up trade.
No, no.
I'm much more worried
about you, Alfonso.
[ALFONSO grunts]
Makin' rounds in this thing
is enough to tire
a man to the bone.
Yeah.
Haven't felt this exhausted
since I can't remember when.
You'd think someone would've
come to see us by now.
A tax collector gets more love.
Maybe people are intimidated.
Could that be it?
Ugh. Waiting around
wasn't what I had in mind
when we built him.
I wanted to be useful,
--not sit around on my haunches
--[knocking]
--all day
--[door opens]
[WOMAN]
Um. Excuse me?
Is this where I'm s'posed to go
if I want to talk to
the Knight of Light?
I need his help. Desperately.
[ALL gasping]
[WOMAN] Every evening,
some kind of demon appears
out of the forest and
terrorizes our farm.
Cattle have been slaughtered,
crops destroyed.
And only yesterday evening,
my poor husband...
We don't need details
if it's painful for you.
We'll take the job.
Whatever this creature is,
we'll wipe it off the
face of the earth.
[MANUEL, PANCHO grunt]
[LARA]
León.
I can scrub your back
for you, if you want.
[LEÓN] Uh, I can manage
on my own, thanks.
[LARA]
You don't have to be like that.
When Papa was around, I used
to wash his back all the time.
Look, I said I could manage.
[LARA gasps]
[LARA]
It'd, uh--
It'd work out a lot better
if your back was to me.
[LARA]
Okay. Here I go, then.
[LARA] You've been a huge help
to us around here, you know.
We're very grateful.
Sure. Least I could do.
Um.
If you had a mind to,
you'd be welcome to stay
with us indefinitely.
[GRANDMA] I tell you, that
young man is hard worker.
He's not much for talk.
He spoke so little I didn't know
what to make of him at first.
Now, though, I can't imagine how
we got along without the boy.
Yes. Perhaps fortune will
smile further and he'll stay.
He and Lara would be a cute--
Oh, well, I ought not
count my chickens.
[GRANDPA]
A wise decision.
He's not the sort to tarry in
one place for long, I'll wager.
His eyes are trouble.
They carry the burden of
having seen terrible things.
Mark my words.
One day, he'll leave.
[howling]
[BRUNO]
Where is the beast?
Must've caught wind
of our presence
and scuttled away in fear.
Easy. It's a bit too
soon to get cocky.
[JULIO]
Stay vigilant.
The sun's only just gone down.
Remember what
the villagers said.
This demon appears under
the cover of darkness.
Julio, would it be all right
if I was off to bed soon?
Anything less than eight
hours of sleep at night
is bad for the skin.
[chuckles]
Huh?
[trees rustling]
[JULIO gasps]
[BEAR growling]
[JULIO]
Here it comes!
That's your cue!
[BRUNO]
Tally-ho!
[BEAR growling]
[roaring]
[grunting]
[yells]
[PETRONA]
Outstanding!
Bruno took the full brunt
of that creature's momentum
and he's still doing just fine!
[MANUEL]
No!
My invincible armor
is fracturing!
[BRUNO]
Damn it, man!
If you must give a running
commentary, be positive!
I'm all the stands
between this monster
and his reign of terror!
This is the village
where he's been seen.
An unlikely location for the
stories we've been hearing.
[BEAR roars]
[ALFONSO]
We must go!
[GERMÁN]
Right.
[BEAR growling]
[grunting]
[BRUNO yells]
[BRUNO]
What? It's a bear!
[EMERICO]
He's stunned!
What're you waiting for?! Finish
it with your special attack!
Wait, special attack?
That wasn't part of our design.
[BRUNO]
Right! Here we go!
Take this, foul thing!
[BRUNO]
Uhh.
Oh, dear!
The Garo Punch doesn't appear
to have made much of an impact.
[BRUNO grunts]
[ALL gasp]
[BRUNO panting]
[ALFONSO]
Do you see it?
[GERMÁN] Yes.
Quite the spectacle.
Huh?
Alfonso, wait, one moment.
I don't believe there's a
role for us to play in this.
The creature is no
more than a bear.
Yes! Now grab on to it
and self-destruct!
What?! That's not--
[gasps]
Señor Bruno! Quick.
Up the pressure to maximum!
The pneumatic
device will explode
and take the bear with it!
Julio! Are you crazy?!
Do you want Bruno to die?!
No, there's an escape hatch.
Trust me. If he wraps
himself around the bear
and slips out through the access
panel we installed in the back,
he'll have time to
clear the blast area
before the suit explodes.
And if the poor man
screws it up, he's dead!
It's all right. Just give
my bones a proper burial.
It's been a pleasure
serving with you.
[BRUNO yelling]
[BRUNO grunting]
Señor Bruno!
You're a tough one, aren't ya?
[BRUNO]
Uh.
Sir Germán!
[ALFONSO yelps]
[ALL]
Hm?
Prince Alfonso?!
What are you doing
all the way out here?
Uh--
You see,
I heard rumors and thought it
would be prudent to investigate.
Then we stumbled across you
engaged in combat with
this behemoth, so...
Fancy His Highness
traveling all the way here.
This'll be a story to
tell your grandchildren.
[ALFONSO]
Come now.
'Tis a prince's duty
to protect his people.
My appearing among you
ought not be so strange.
Hm.
At any rate,
good work, all of you.
I am deeply impressed.
[GERMÁN chuckles]
[grunts]
[BLACKSMITHS chattering]
[MAN]
Uh, excuse me.
Not to put a damper on the mood,
but if someone could help
me put out this fire,
that'd be helpful.
It's just shy of the barn.
[GERMÁN] Never underestimate
the people we protect.
They are anything but weak.
Their strength abides
in the everyday.
The ebb and flow of life itself.
[ALFONSO]
Yes.
Precisely why I'm devoted.
I wish to see them thrive.
[GARM]
Alas, once planted and watered,
a blossom finds
the hand that tends,
and the hand that plucks,
are one and the same.