[GERMÁN] That's it for me.
This body's had enough.
I'd be careful if I were you.
Just so happens
my son is up there.
León Luís.
You may have heard of him.
[GERMÁN]
It is in his blood
to protect this world
from such as you.
Legend calls him
the Golden Knight...
Garo!
[HORRORS growl]
[GERMÁN]
I know his strength.
God, do I know it. [groans]
For he is my son and no
father has ever been prouder.
You may call me Germán Luís.
Makai Knight.
Also known by the name...
Zoro.
[HORRORS growl]
[XIMENA]
Germán.
[CITIZENS worried chatter]
--[CITIZENS worried chatter]
--[XIMENA] Mm?
[CITIZEN A]
The end is nigh!
[CITIZEN B] Behold! The moon!
Look at the moon!
[CITIZEN C]
It's being devoured by a demon!
[CITIZEN A]
Merciful God! Deliver us!
[XIMENA panting]
You idiot.
--[rattling]
--[LEÓN] Uh?!
[LEÓN]
Jiruba?
[OCTAVIA growls]
[GHOSTLY VOICES scream]
The hour is upon us.
The time of fruition.
Good evening, Prince Alfonso,
and the rest of you.
How far you've managed to
come by your own power.
Such interminable pests.
[ALFONSO, LEÓN gasp]
Aren't you that lady in waiting?
So your position
was a mere ploy.
I bought it completely, nicely
done. Joke's on us, eh?
Clearly you're a woman
of singular conviction
and many faces.
[ALFONSO]
Why? How could you?
My mother and father
trusted in you!
They drew strength
from your loyalty.
Come, Your Highness. 'Tis folly
to cast tears over treachery.
Do not imagine I held
a grudge against them.
My devotion to Master Mendoza
takes pride of place, is all.
He is the pulse of my heart.
In him, I am more than
a lady in waiting.
[ALFONSO whimpers]
[OCTAVIA] Compared to his
grand vision, of course,
I am but a speck of
dust. However....
[LEÓN] I have neither the
time nor the patience
for your chatter.
My father's waiting.
Now stand aside!
All apologies, sir knight.
I cannot allow you to pass.
You will go no further!
[LEÓN yells]
[OCTAVIA grunts]
[ZARUBA] She is encased in
Majuu Armor. Mind its strength!
Majuu Armor?
That's quite a rarity.
--[OCTAVIA gasps]
--[LEÓN grunts]
[EMA gasps]
[ALFONSO groans]
[LEÓN grunts]
[EMA]
León!
You're a fool.
Those vestments are
forged by pure hatred.
The price that Majuu Armor will
exact from its wearer is dear.
Even now, you...
[gasps]
[panting]
Oh, Master Mendoza!
I live only for you!
How I've longed to clasp your
hand! To know your sweet touch!
Thank you, Master!
[OCTAVIA gasping]
[ALFONSO grunts]
[EMA]
Mm.
[OCTAVIA moans]
[ALFONSO yells]
[LEÓN]
Alfonso!
Ema!
[LEÓN gasps]
[EMA]
Listen to me.
You must swear not to
give in to the fire.
You protect. Whatever happens,
that is who you are.
I swear.
[LEÓN sighs]
Uh!
[HORRORS roar]
[ZARUBA] Be ready. Horrors
approach in great number!
[ALFONSO groans]
[ALFONSO gasps]
[OCTAVIA]
Worry not, master! I am coming!
[OCTAVIA gasps]
[EMA] I see exile left your
master no less capable
of astonishing things.
[OCTAVIA gasps]
Incidentally...
Do you think he'd mind that
I borrowed this from his room?
[OCTAVIA]
Base thief! Ah!
[LEÓN growls]
[LEÓN yells]
[LEÓN]
Hey, old man! Where are you?
It's me. I'm here!
I came as Jiruba instructed!
Talk to me! Hey!
[LEÓN]
Where the hell are you?
Damn it, answer me!
[LEÓN sighs]
Where are you?
--[MENDOZA] Bravo.
--[LEÓN] Uh!
[MENDOZA] I underestimated
your determination.
To think that you've broken
through multiple barriers.
You've matured
since last we spoke.
Mendoza!
He says my name in anger,
and again deigns to
raise his blade at me.
Are we back to where
we started, boy?
So it must be.
But before you act in haste,
I suggest you look below me.
[gasps]
[MENDOZA]
Tragic, yes?
I give you what's left
of your valiant father.
Uh!
Old Man...
[ALFONSO, OCTAVIA grunting]
[EMA yells]
[ALFONSO yells]
[OCTAVIA screams]
This is our chance!
Release the seal!
[EMA, ALFONSO gasp]
[EMA]
Son of a... You must be joking!
[OCTAVIA yells]
That was unexpected.
Not very sporting of you.
[panting] Germán, please...
[gasps]
[XIMENA]
The prince?
[XIMENA gasps, pants]
[MENDOZA]
So very close.
If only you'd come
a moment earlier,
you'd have had the pleasure of
watching the brave man die.
His limbs cleft from him
by a legion of Horrors.
Anointed in his blood.
A wrenching death if ever
there was one, rest assured.
Be happy, young knight! He
and your whore of a mother
shall both rise above
their petty circumstances
to be consumed by Anima.
Cat got your tongue?
Words fail to capture
your feelings?
Will you not weep and gnash
your teeth at the memory
of a father who died waiting?
Oh. Perhaps your grief
renders you unable to move?
I almost pity you.
[HORRORS growl]
So, I take it this is
all you have to say?
What?
[HORROR B growls]
[HORROR A growls]
[MENDOZA gasps]
[XIMENA screams]
[CAMILLO] Ximena!
What are you doing out here?
It's dangerous!
[XIMENA]
Señor Camillo!
Come! Things will only get
worse. We need to evacuate!
Help me round up whomever
we can and get them out!
[gasps]
Very well!
[ALFONSO grunts]
[OCTAVIA, ALFONSO grunting]
[ALFONSO yells]
[EMA yells]
[LEÓN]
No more will I falter.
No more will I be
twisted by your words.
No more will I burn.
I am a protector!
I will be the end of your story!
[MENDOZA]
Ooh. Best of luck to you, then.
[HORRORS squelching]
[HORRORS roar]
[LEÓN grunting]
[LEÓN growls]
Ah. Zoro, you damn fool.
Though I am the bigger fool
for thinking you would
be equal to this task.
Ah, well. 'Tis neither here
nor there. Let it be done.
Garm means business.
The hourglass has run out.
[ALFONSO]
I will stop it!
[EMA]
Uh!
Miss Ema, I need you to get
me to the Watchdog Center!
Alfonso. You can't
possibly think...
I'm not asking.
--[HORRORS growl]
--[LEÓN grunting]
[LEÓN yells]
[LEÓN]
Mendoza!
[MENDOZA]
Mm. Well, that's a shame.
I had hoped to add the Golden
Knight to the sacrificial altar.
[LEÓN grunts]
[MENDOZA]
I fear it is too late.
[LEÓN gasps]
[MENDOZA]
Anima is awakening!
Do it! Now!
[EMA]
Hold your damn horses.
I'll ask one last time...
Are you absolutely sure?
[ALFONSO] Either I protect
the people of this kingdom,
or I am no Makai Knight!
Yeah, well asinine thoughts
like that will get one killed.
See, this is why I
loathe you people.
[ZARUBA] León! The Gates
of Makai are opening!
[HORRORS roar]
[LEÓN] This thing is devouring
the Horrors cascading out of it.
[OCTAVIA]
Damn the Makai Knights!
Look out! Behind you!
[EMA] Don't worry about it...
just go! I'll deal with her!
Right!
[yells]
[ALFONSO yells]
[OCTAVIA growls]
[EMA grunts]
[OCTAVIA groaning]
I'm afraid this is the end.
[OCTAVIA]
Indeed. For you!
[gasps]
[ALFONSO grunting]
[ALFONSO yells]
[panting]
[OCTAVIA groans]
--[OCTAVIA screams]
--[panting]
[OCTAVIA screams]
Your body has reached its limit.
The armor ruthlessly
carves away
at every aspect of the
wearer's being.
Look at yourself.
Was the power worth
living on borrowed time?
No, I think not.
Do you now see Mendoza
for what he is?
How he rewards your loyalty?
You've been used up.
Cast-off like a fouled garment.
'Tis only what I wished for.
Prayed for.
Say what you will. He never
scorned to answer me.
How could I not give my
all in return? He is a god!
I am gifted with
an honorable death.
I leave in an
ecstasy of purpose!
You are not qualified
to pass judgment on me!
You and your ilk would cast-off
the people of this kingdom
in service to what it pleases
you to call your mission.
And you have the gall to
think yourselves protectors?
We do at that.
But not in service of those
fools at the Watchdog Center.
We stand alone.
What we do now flies in the
face of our superiors' will.
[EMA] We fight not for
the Watchdog Center,
but for the people.
If we die honorably,
it will be to protect them.
[OCTAVIA screaming]
A damn waste. You
could've been so much.
[GARM sighs]
[ALFONSO yells]
[GARM]
Good gracious.
This is why Makai Knights
are so tiresome.
Well, you had better
clean up after yourselves.
[MENDOZA]
Such beauty! At last.
Hell inherits the world
of man. Thank you.
The Makai Knights
have done well.
Anima might've slept
indefinitely.
I applaud you, boy.
[LEÓN grunts]
[LEÓN grunting]
[LEÓN gasps]
[LEÓN]
Father.
[ANIMA growls]
[GARM]
The iron will of our forebears.
The burden of heritage.
A fire that burns from
everlasting to everlasting.