[LEÓN]
I couldn't have heard you right!
[ALFONSO]
You don't seriously mean that?
Is it even possible
the man lives?!
[GERMÁN] Surprise, surprise.
Miracles never cease.
It is.
[LEÓN]
You're out your mind!
Even if he is alive,
why would you help him?!
[GERMÁN] Because the
Watchdog Center tells me to.
The idea actually
has some merit.
Being a protector
works both ways.
I didn't want you to fret
over what came of ol' Germán.
[ALFONSO]
Uncle, please!
[GERMÁN]
Now, promise not to follow.
[LEÓN]
Old man!
Wait!
[ALFONSO]
Hm.
[ALFONSO sighs]
[gasps]
[LAURA gasps]
--[ALFONSO] Uh.
--[LAURA] Ah!
[ALFONSO]
Forgive my carelessness.
[LAURA] Uh! I-I'm sorry,
your Highness!
The fault was mine entirely!
I ought to have moved.
[OCTAVIA]
Our apologies, Your Grace.
You attend to the king.
My utmost gratitude, ma'am.
You do me a great honor.
Uh, yes! A great honor!
[ALFONSO chuckles]
[sighs] Well, that
was unexpected.
Uh... uh!
Laura. You are a
lady-in-waiting.
Pray, look sharp.
Yes! Look sharp!
Thank you, Miss Octavia.
Sorry.
[MAID A] How many times
must that girl be told?
One does not envy Octavia
having such a novice
constantly underfoot.
God's truth, she's not worth
the breath to scold.
Thank heavens! Miss Ema! León!
You're unharmed!
Forgive me, Alfonso,
but there was no reason
for you to worry about me.
Your injuries rather
give the lie to that.
And what's become of your hair?
[EMA]
I'll ignore that last remark.
But if by injuries you mean
these minor scratches,
I have just the thing.
She's slowly pickling herself.
Is that so? Who are
you to criticize?
Someone who cares more for
your health than you do!
Uh, now now friends!
Other matters require
our attention.
Please, come inside.
So, cousin.
Did she fare as well
as you hoped?
Should I even know what
that is intended to mean?!
Oh. Have I offended you?
If you'll allow it,
I'm more than happy to
answer in the boy's place.
Shut your mouth!
I've been given to
understand she's hunted
that particular Horror
for quite some time.
Oh, uh. It's over now.
She did her duty admirably.
[ALFONSO]
I see.
Well. That's a blessing.
[LEÓN sighs]
I know my old man.
He probably made
the whole thing up.
[ALFONSO]
No.
I beg your pardon, but not
even he's that careless.
And lest we forget,
Mendoza's a gifted Alchemist.
It's possible he
crafted some illusion
whereby he only
appeared to have died.
His conjurings are vivid.
When we fought, I'd never
seen anything like them.
I've been investigating
on my own.
Thus far, I've rifled
through his old quarters.
And down in the cellar where
Zirkiel's Circle was stored.
Alas, I haven't yet searched
the subterranean temple.
[LEÓN]
That place.
I wouldn't be surprised
to find something there.
There's also a maid.
Her name is Octavia.
What about her?
She is a lady-in-waiting,
responsible for the
care of my father.
Last night, quite late,
she was seen leaving
the palace chapel.
So, can we not assume
the woman was praying?
[ALFONSO] Perhaps, but her
doing so in the dead of night,
alone, seems worthy of note.
The chapel connects with
the underground temple.
You are a godsend, Octavia.
Truly. Where would I be
without your kindness?
[OCTAVIA]
I am flattered, Your Majesty.
[MAID B] His Highness,
Prince Alfonso, Your Grace.
Let him come in.
[footsteps]
[ALFONSO]
Father!
I've brought the friends
I was telling you about,
if you've the strength
for company.
What say you?
May they come in?
Ha! Of course.
Please. Bid them to enter.
León. Miss Ema.
[LEÓN]
León Luís, Your Majesty.
[EMA] Ema Guzmán,
it's indeed an honor.
Yes. You've helped my son
in times of great need.
I've looked forward
to meeting you both.
Sire. If I may be so bold,
I presumed to bring
Your Highness tribute.
Wine. From the vineyards
of Paolagena.
Famed far and wide for
its medicinal properties.
[OCTAVIA gasps]
I cordially accept
your offering.
A word of caution Sire,
sufficient quantities
can numb the senses.
Duly noted, young lady.
That may be the quickest
way to recover.
[EMA, FERNANDO laugh]
[LEÓN]
She certainly isn't a Horror.
[ALFONSO]
No.
Perhaps my suspicions
were unfounded.
For now, though, let
us think of dinner.
You must be famished
from travel.
Please, won't you
dine with me tonight?
Oh! Oh, my, I couldn't turn
down such royal hospitality.
I won't make you insist.
You'll want us to stay
the night as well?
[LAURA] May I ask a question,
Lady Octavia? I, uh...
Sorry, I shouldn't babble.
Out with it, girl.
Um, well you see...
I was curious as to your
opinion of Prince Alfonso.
Oh, dear! I'm sorry!
It's terribly presumptuous
of me to ask!
I'm simply overwhelmed
by the kindness
he showed me this afternoon.
That kindness had nothing
to do with you,
it is simply in his nature.
Don't read so much into it.
No, yes, of course, ma'am.
I understand perfectly.
But bearing that in mind.
You care for His Majesty's every
need, supposing he were to,
that is to say, if he asked--
Yes. Without a second thought.
[gasps]
They say to covet is a sin,
but even ladies in waiting
may dream of better
for themselves.
Uh... Yes, but dreaming a
thing doesn't make it so.
Believe me, Laura.
I am aware.
[LAURA gasps]
One almost covets your
simple-mindedness.
Well, I never...!
[ORLETTA]
Do you hear what comes
out of your mouth, Tavia?!
[OCTAVIA]
Should the King ever see fit
to take me as a wife, you
can be my lady in waiting.
[LAURA]
Uh! You don't mean that?!
Of course you don't,
you're only teasing me.
I assure you I'm not.
Loyalty is dear, I prefer the
company of those I may count on.
Oh, but, Surely there is
someone more capable than me?
Truth be told, Laura,
you remind me of someone.
[LAURA]
Uh?!
Let's finish clearing the table,
there's something special
I'm eager for you to see.
[footsteps]
Good evening, Octavia.
[OCTAVIA] I've brought
you something to eat.
It is a meager repast, to be
sure, and for that I am sorry.
I do not mind.
His Highness the Prince
moves ever closer.
May I ask if we really
intend to leave the boy be?
He and his comrades amuse me.
Let the retinue of fools
occupy themselves
as they please, I am impervious.
I care not the cost,
I will not allow them
to cause you the
slightest inconvenience.
Even if it means
sacrificing my life.
[MENDOZA]
Do not speak of death
as though it's what
I wish for you.
[gasps]
[MENDOZA]
Octavia. You are my servant.
Please, am I to toss you
aside like battered toy?
[OCTAVIA sighs]
Take care to stay alive.
'Twould cause no end
of inconvenience
should you be cleft from me.
I understand, sir.
--[ALFONSO] Where were you?
--[WOMAN gasps]
Do not think to answer
me with silence.
Would you dare play the mute?
[LAURA gasps] I know this looks
terribly questionable, but-- Uh!
Laura, what are you...?!
[screams]
What is the meaning
of all this?
I'm so sorry! I didn't mean to!
I, uh, I'll clean
this up at once!
That's not what I meant.
What is someone like you
doing in a place like this?
[LAURA] I-I was collecting water
from an underground spring.
It was discovered not long
after the castle was damaged.
Water began bubbling up
from one of the broken
flagstones down here.
I can't tell you the last time
I've known water of this purity.
So, we're using it
in the King's meals.
Oddly enough,
it dries up at sunrise.
It has quite a clean taste.
How did you find this place?
I'm not the one
who found it, sire.
It was my Lady Octavia.
Lady Octavia?!
[LAURA]
Yes, sir.
She mentioned having discovered
it during the reconstruction.
[ALFONSO sighs]
Interesting.
She thought it prudent
to collect water
herself at first, you see.
However, recently,
we've been taking turns.
The care she gives to
His Majesty commands
so much of her time.
Is that so? Clearly measures
must be taken to increase
the number of servants.
Oh! You don't have to!
I wasn't complaining, really!
I didn't think you were.
[sighs] Thank goodness.
Oh! I mean...
that is to say, um...
You... seem to get thrown
out of sorts rather easily.
A calmer demeanor might
be worth cultivating.
I hear that a lot.
[chuckles] I'm sure you do.
[ALFONSO] Sorry to have
given you such a start.
Treat yourself
to a spot of rest.
Thank you! That would be
wonderful, Your Highness!
I apologize if this exchange
has inconvenienced you.
Good night!
[ALFONSO]
Mm... Good night.
[EMA] There's no sign
the seal's been broken.
All right, friends.
Let's see what terrors await us.
Uh?!
Ah. I'll just take
the rear, then.
Oh, my I've never felt more
like a princess in my life!
[LEÓN] Pillars once
stood here, I believe.
[ALFONSO] I suspect so,
but they were gone
before Miss Ema and
I sealed the entry.
In all likelihood,
Mendoza created them to
summon the Makai beast.
[EMA] As if my flesh weren't
already crawling.
We should've paid attention
the last time we were here.
Indeed.
[ALFONSO]
What's wrong?
[EMA gasps]
Zaruba, do you sense
anything at all?
Nothing out of the ordinary, no.
Just a fancy.
Let us go.
[EMA exhales]
You really expect Mendoza
to be on the castle grounds?
I'd have a better idea
if I could speak to
uncle on the matter.
[LEÓN] Maybe we should
interrogate Garm?
And waste our time?
'Twould be a much finer thing
to douse ourselves in drink
and let the clues seek us.
[MENDOZA]
Excellent. Admittedly,
I was fretful of Zaruba and the
meddlesome Makai Alchemist.
Our reservations were
unfounded, master.
[MENDOZA]
So it would seem.
I am amused at the effort spent
creating such a powerful
barrier in the first place.
Their suspicions are quickly
dropping by the wayside.
[MENDOZA]
I am pleased to hear it.
[knocking]
I shall be in touch.
[LAURA]
It's Laura.
Yes. You may enter.
The bath has been drawn and is
ready for His Majesty, ma'am.
That's excellent.
And, were there any problems?
None to speak of!
For the moment, all is well.
In that case, report back
to me only after His Majesty
has retired to bed. Later
tonight, I shall look in on him.
Uh. Yes, ma'am. Very good.
[OCTAVIA]
And Laura?
Uh, yes?
Carry yourself with confidence.
Should you misstep,
be willing to learn from it.
[LAURA]
Mm. Thank you.
[gasps]
Uh!
[EMA gasps]
[gasps]
León! Hurry up! Quickly!
[ALFONSO]
Which way?!
Above us!
Is that possible?!
[LEÓN grunts]
Damn it!
[OCTAVIA whimpering]
[OCTAVIA] I'm telling you I've
been praying every single day.
If he was capable of saving us,
he'da done it by now.
I never...!
Do you hear what comes
out of your mouth?
Lucky for you, God is
merciful to wayward souls.
I'd watch myself, though.
[OCTAVIA panting]
[WOLVES growling]
[MAN screaming]
[WOMAN screams]
[OCTAVIA]
Orletta! Don't just stand there!
Run!
Those things'll
rip you to shreds!
[ORLETTA]
Octavia!
What are you waiting for?
Get out of there!
You must have faith!
God will save us!
Believe it in your
heart of hearts!
We have but to wait.
We pray every day!
He'll show us mercy!
I know He will! Please, Tavia!
For once, you must
have faith in Him!
I promise He will save us.
--You'll see!
--[OCTAVIA panting]
[OCTAVIA grunts]
[MENDOZA] I will never
discard you, my dear.
This I swear.
For when you've exhausted
all other options.
An act of bloodletting will
suffice to release it.
[OCTAVIA whimpering]
My Lady Octavia!
[LAURA]
Ma'am? What's happened?
[whimpering]
[OCTAVIA]
Uh!
--[LAURA gasps]
--[HORRORS growl]
I command you to
consume the girl!
[gasps] No!
[OCTAVIA whimpers]
[OCTAVIA]
Your Majesty!
Laura has become a monster!
Fear not! I will protect you!
[HORRORS growl]
[OCTAVIA]
Now bite off my right leg.
I command you!
[HORRORS growl]
[OCTAVIA screams]
Octavia, no!
[EMA gasps]
I'd say we've found it.
[LEÓN yells]
What the...?!
[HORRORS growl]
[OCTAVIA] I command
you to attack me again!
We have to take it on all sides!
I'll take the left!
[ALFONSO]
Understood!
[ALFONSO, LEÓN growl]
[ALFONSO, LEÓN roar]
--[WOLVES growl]
--[ORLETTA screams]
Help us, please!
My sister is still inside!
We can't just leave her!
[VILLAGER A] But we can't fight
a pack of bloodthirsty wolves!
Everyone run for your lives,
and don't look back!
No, wait! You can't!
Don't go! Help us!
Don't just...
don't just throw us away.
Please, God!
Save us.
[ALFONSO]
You're awake. Thank heavens.
Everything's all right now.
Is His Majesty safe?
Thanks in no small part
to your courage, yes.
I didn't realize Laura was...
Father and I have
just had a word.
Forgive me, please,
but I have to ask,
did anything about her strike
you as odd before tonight?
Would that it had, my prince.
I know.
The mind struggles
to believe it of her.
Your Highness.
May I be allowed to
rest now, please?
Yes. Of course.
I'm very sorry for what you've
had to endure tonight, Octavia.
Thank you for so bravely
protecting my father.
[door opens, closes]
[OCTAVIA whimpering]
[LAURA laughs]
[OCTAVIA sobs]
Damn them all.
Damn them to hell!
May the Makai Knights
burn for all eternity!
[LEÓN] Well, whoever was
here, they clearly used
another way to make
their escape.
Yes, there may be a
number of other ways
in and out of which
we know nothing.
I suggest another sweep
of the underground temple
with all due haste.
[GERMÁN] About that, I'll thank
you all to leave it be.
There you are!
Dammit, old man.
Let's be plain. Continue to
pursue this line of inquiry
and things will get
unpleasant.
Will you just do me the
kindness of retreating now?
[LEÓN exhales]
Of course not.
What would possess me to think
you would listen to your father?
If you don't get
out of our way...
old man...
I will cut you down.
[laughs] That's quite the
look of determination
you've got there,
son. Come on, then.
[GARM] Two fangs,
clashing with one another.
Their hope for the future,
one and the same.
Dear, oh dear.