Master.
[LEÓN]
Alfonso?
Let me help you
build a grave marker.
Thank you, but I'll
wield this blade
and don his armor in
tribute to his legacy.
His memory defends me,
as this sword does, and every
day I shall honor him with it.
As you honor the
blood of your mother
with the sword you bear, León.
Huh? You knew?
You knew the
whole time, didn't you?
[ALFONSO]
You are the Golden Knight, Garo.
A title of legend.
You are a myth, a hero
spoken of in countless stories.
All those that live beneath
Valiante's skies know the name.
[LEÓN sighs]
Such titles are only words.
I'm simply a Makai Knight
with aims to slay
Mendoza and his Horrors.
Yes, and that
is all that I am.
True or not,
you and I are both striving
toward the same goal.
Upon my sword I vow:
We will rid our fair
country of Mendoza.
Valiante will be free again.
Come! Let us so swear.
Huh?
[sighs] Right!
[EMA] You do so love
to put yourself in danger.
It actually pains me.
[LEÓN]
Ema!
Doing well, León?
What the hell?
Really? Is that how
you choose to address
the person who
just saved your life?
Thank you. I'm...
I'm in your debt.
Next time, why don't
you try looking me
in the eyes when
you say that, chico?
Now, thank me proper.
[grunts] I owe you my life!
Now get your hands off me!
That'll do. So...
Why would you risk life and limb
just to come back to this place?
I doubt you're here for
that naked fool of a father.
[LEÓN]
Hey, you in there?
You're back!
I found the supplies
we'll require
and something to eat, too.
[ALFONSO]
Thank you, León.
It's good to see you safe.
[LEÓN]
Safe is not how I'd put it.
You see--
[ALFONSO] Tell me, did you
happen to find your father
in the city as well?
I am quite anxious to
know that he's all right.
[gasps]
That idiot doesn't
deserve the name "father."
[ALFONSO] Come, I won't
have you speaking ill of the man
who's technically my uncle--
Who goes there?!
A simple Makai Alchemist
by the name of Ema Guzman.
It's such a pleasure
to finally meet you, Sire.
An alchemist?
You too fight for the freedom of
this land? I beg your pardon.
You are ever welcome here.
[EMA] Worry not,
Alfonso, pardon granted.
Now then.
I believe you said Germán is
your uncle, if I'm not mistaken.
He's an empty cask of a man,
ever beholden to his rudder,
so if it's true,
you have my condolences.
--[LEÓN sighs]
--[ALFONSO] Uh... Thank you?
[CUCKOLDED HUSBAND A]
Hold it right there,
you accursed weasel!
[GERMÁN] Wait! Just wait!
I can explain, I swear!
I was just helping your wife
with her stiff shoulders.
It's a serious problem!
[CUCKOLDED HUSBAND A]
That doesn't do a damned thing
to explain your own stiffness.
[GERMÁN chuckles]
Well, no, maybe not!
Ah! Look over there,
a witch soaring past!
She's naked as a jaybird!
[CUCKOLDED HUSBAND A]
Where?
Dammit! Where'd
that snake run off to?
What kind of woman would
marry a man like that?
Oh. Good morning, everyone.
The hell were you thinking?
[GERMÁN]
Hmmm...
Stay your hand, León.
This rake IS your father.
If that can even be possible.
Sad but true, young prince.
Who are you, exactly?
Oh. Right.
Please, call me Alfonso.
I'm a Makai Knight, descended
of Garo, like your son, here.
Huh...? "Descended
of Garo." But how?!
It can't be! Impossible!
Still, you do have her eyes.
Hey!
Could it be?
Could my sweet Anna have
loved another in secret?
Tell me, quickly, what kind
of man was your father?
[ALFONSO]
Uh...
No, speak not another word!
Will you stop spouting
nonsense for one second?
[GERMÁN]
No matter.
You are a son of my beloved Anna
and I will raise you as my own.
[LEÓN]
What?
[GERMÁN]
I must be alone.
There is much to think on.
[EMA laughs]
Who'd have thought the
consummate home-wrecker
had such a glass jaw?
This is all a misunderstanding.
We must put his mind to rest.
Let him stew a bit.
[ALFONSO] But--
She's right, though it's
hardly punishment enough
for all the crap he's pulled.
How can he doubt Mother when
he finds a new bed every night?
He loves her so much that
it's impossible to trust her.
[chuckles] He's almost
cute all flustered.
[GERMÁN]
My Anna.
How could you keep
another love from me?
Was I not man enough?
[sobs]
Santa Bard's Royal
Palace is built
upon the ruins of an old temple.
There should still be an
entrance tucked away
somewhere near the
base of the eastern cliff.
Through the temple,
there's a tunnel,
which connects to
the bowels of the castle.
It once served as
a royal escape route,
and with any luck,
it's still undefended.
[EMA] Maybe,
but Mendoza is certainly
aware of its existence.
[ALFONSO] Yes, perhaps,
but it's far less risky
than attacking
head on. However...
What?
Surely the castle is filled to
the brim with Mendoza's Horrors.
We have no way of
knowing what awaits us.
[EMA] Nothing good.
He controls the Horrors by use
of a forbidden Madou tool,
Zirkiel's Circle.
He stole it from the council.
It functions like the rings you
wear but on a grander scale.
[BERNARDO] The Orvien
Chimera has been slain
at the hand of our
little prince Alfonso.
Another soul to the ranks
of the Makai Knighthood.
[MENDOZA sighs]
[MENDOZA] I put one down
and yet another rises.
Such curs are naught
but mindless dogs,
good only for hunting
and birthing more.
Though, Rafael's death
comes as welcome news to me.
I am glad of your victory.
I pity the ground stained
by his filthy Makai blood.
Death has taken all those
who stood in judgment.
[YOUNGER MENDOZA]
Excommunication?
For serving our order,
you would see me exiled from it?
I have created a miracle!
A Madou tool of
infinite potential!
You saw my results,
you saw what it can do!
[MASTER]
Silence, do not speak.
That which you call
a miracle, Mendoza,
is but defilement and betrayal.
Your vile use of human blood
breaks our most sacred pact,
for we are sworn
above all things to guard
and keep mortal life.
Our pact is so
ancient it crumbles!
We are more than humanity could
ever dare dream of becoming!
Why should we
kneel at their feet?
Why should we serve?!
Let us rule over them
and see their precious
freedom brought low!
They should beg and scrape
for the privilege of
bleeding at our hands!
How I pity you, Mendoza.
You are blind to
your sins, even now.
Were we not fettered by our
oath, you would meet your end.
However, we may brand you
as chastisement
for your corruption.
But Master!
My tool can do more
than you've seen!
It can grant you eternal life!
You are long lost, alchemist.
It is in the birth of new life
that mankind achieves eternity.
[MENDOZA]
You fool!
[MASTER] We purge our
order of your tainted blood.
Never again will
it cross our own.
Written in thy veins
shall be this mark.
Seared upon thy children
and thy children's children.
Eternally shall they inherit
the punishment for your sin.
[MENDOZA]
Why, master?
Why have you forsaken me? Why?
[YOUNGER MENDOZA]
Damn you!
I will see you suffer
for every mark on my skin!
Your name is Mendoza?
I understand you're
the one whose medicines
saved my fair city from
the ravages of the plague.
Many thanks.
Yes, Your Majesty.
[FERNANDO]
You are a wanderer, yes? A sage?
It would give me great pleasure
to have you stay a while.
Why don't you enter my
service here at the castle?
I will serve with
pride, Highness.
[FERNANDO]
Mendoza! Hahaha!
Ah, good to see you, my friend!
I bring happy news!
Haha! Your strategy
was a great success!
The battle's won! I owe this
conquest to your advice!
I live to serve, my liege.
Your wisdom is unparalleled--
you must have been
blessed with divine insight
to know that their army
would fall to our assault.
Blessed with the might
of Horrors, my good lord.
Huh?
[MENDOZA]
Nothing.
Well, 'tis fine!
Just see to it that
you keep my rewards
as close as you keep
your many secrets.
M'lady, please join us inside!
[gasps]
Meet your wife.
This young maid is
Angelina--eldest daughter
of my esteemed bannerman,
the Count of Gostilia.
I confess it a part of my plot
to keep you ever at my side,
Mendoza! Hahahaha!
[woman screaming]
[MIDWIFE A]
Huh? No. Please, sir.
You mustn't come closer. Ah!
[sobs]
[MASTER] We purge our
order of your tainted blood.
Never again will
it cross our own.
Written in thy veins
shall be this mark.
Seared upon thy children
and thy children's children.
Amor.
Accursed Makai...
Knights, Alchemists...
I shall sever clean
your bloodlines
from this earth
'til not one remains!
Who approaches?
You're the handmaid
to Her Highness.
[OCTAVIA] My name
is Octavia, good lord.
[MENDOZA]
Why do you come to me?
I was raised to
believe in God,
a Master I have
never laid eyes on,
but each day I have seen
demons that bring suffering,
with no intervention
from Heaven.
But your coldness,
your strength,
this is a power
I can believe in.
The Horrors, then.
You saw them, girl?
[gasps] Is that the
title you gave them?
Your God's betrayal
still lingers within you.
Do you forsake all other oaths,
and swear fealty to me?
[OCTAVIA]
Yes.
I am yours within and
without, I do so swear.
[MENDOZA]
Octavia.
Listen well to my words.
I shall never forsake you,
nor ever discard you.
Your God, in His
arrogance, already has.
But you are not permitted to
ever lay your hand upon me.
[MENDOZA]
Bernardo. I have faith
that your knights will locate
the traitorous prince soon.
Ensure it is done
with no mistakes.
Maybe the boy will give
me a fight worth my time.
Not yet.
Choose well the place
you'll cut him down.
Hmph.
[MENDOZA]
Come along.
We have much to prepare
for the hero's return.
[GERMÁN sighs]
Oh, Anna.
Was our perfect
love just a façade?
And what then of León?
Did he inherit your
hidden hatred for me?
Oh! Whoa! Ahh...
[sighs]
Hey! What was that for?
Just shocking you
out of your depression.
Let's go.
But you very nearly
killed me! [growls]
[ALFONSO chuckles]
Eh... Where're we off to?
[LEÓN] A secret passage
into the castle.
If you are not opposed,
I'll lead the way.
I believe you said
your name was Alfonso.
[ALFONSO]
Sir.
First, I apologize.
This time alone helped me to
put order to my manly thinking.
Uh?
[GERMÁN]
You're still Anna's blood,
no matter the father, and
I will raise you like my own.
We've got a lot of lost
time to make up for, son.
Thank you, but, I, uh...
[LEÓN]
Seriously?
What kind of idiot are you?
We don't share the
same mother, you moron!
[GERMÁN]
Wha?
[GERMÁN laughs]
Of course! I get it!
Of course she
had a little sister!
I knew all along Anna would
never have betrayed me!
How did this never come up?
She was probably so lost
in my eyes, she just forgot.
Hey, hold on
just a minute there.
That would make me the
uncle to the heir apparent
of Valiante's throne which,
in turn, would make me
almost a part of
the royal bloodline!
Now! Let us strike fast and
capture Santa Bard Castle!
As uncle to Valiante's
beloved prince-in-exile,
I'll have my royal hands
full of all the handmaidens!
Maybe a harem!
[GERMÁN screams]
How'd he make
it down so fast?
We should catch up.
Here. And up you go.
You're a great help.
[GERMÁN sneezes]
We'll begin scouting
at the top, Uncle.
Yeah, I'm right behind ya.
Just give me a minute.
Germán, do you think
that boy can handle it?
Hmm? Well, he's faced much
since this mad quest began.
It's nice to see that you're
worried about León, though.
There's danger in
those marks on his skin.
Over time, he may succumb.
Oh? So you noticed that?
I notice much.
They respond aggressively when
his passions run the hottest.
The flames protect him,
yet that same inferno
could burn him to cinders.
I've no doubt the fire's
a trait of his mother.
All the rest is a mystery,
save that it's dangerous
and we can't do a
damn thing about it.
[LEÓN] Come on!
We don't have all day!
Wait. Are you not
along for the ride?
My role in this siege
has already been played.
Besides, I know
the thing I'm hunting
won't be found in Santa Bard.
Hunting, you say?
I've a Horror in mind.
Look who's got a mysterious
back-story ferretted away.
I should've known.
My apologies.
I'll leave charging into
certain death up to you, sir.
Certain death always
sounded kinda romantic to me.
Hey, if I do make it outta here,
why don't we have a drink?
With that sentiment, you won't.
So you know,
I'm gonna go ahead
and count that as a yes!
Only if I'm up for it.
Ah...
I never thought I'd
come home this way.
What of your mother?
If she's being held captive
inside the castle somewhere,
do you know where she'd be?
Yes.
They'd have moved her
to the Prisoner's Tower.
There's only one entrance,
and the bridge is always held.
[LEÓN] Right.
We make for the bridge.
We cannot.
I want my mother freed,
but I returned to save Valiante.
Huh?
[ALFONSO]
My land must come first.
My mother would say the
same thing in my place.
Even while imprisoned.
It is the truth.
This is the way of kings.
But I am grateful.
[SOLDIER 10A]
Well. Any change?
[SOLDIER 10B] None. She's still
quiet as the grave. [yawns]]
[SOLDIER 10A]
We must be vigilant.
Rumor is Prince Alfonso
has appeared in town.
[SOLDIER 10B]
He came back?
[SOLDIER 10A] Should he
come to rescue the Queen,
we won't survive the day.
Mendoza wants her ready to move
in case she must be
used to trump the prince.
[SOLDIER 10B]
Damn.
Of all the days to
get stuck guarding her.
[ESMERALDA]
My son.
For Valiante's future, you must
see through the devil's traps.
This I pray!
[LEÓN] What are those?
There must be dozens of them.
They are certainly not ancient
enough to be part of the temple.
Which means all of this,
everything, has fallen
under Mendoza's spell.
[ALFONSO]
The Royal Tomb.
This is where the temple
and the palace become one.
Well this is a suitably creepy
foundation for the castle above.
I'm not sure I could sleep at
night knowing this was here.
[LEÓN]
Hmm?
What was that sound just now?
[ALFONSO]
I've never seen this place.
[LEÓN]
That smell is like rotted meat!
What the hell has Mendoza
been up to, hiding down here?
Nothing pleasant,
I can assure you.
We should keep moving.
[LEÓN]
Damn!
Come on, we keep
heading for the top!
[GERMÁN]
Right.
[LEÓN]
Horrors!
[ALFONSO]
Uncle!
[LEÓN]
Come on!
[ALFONSO]
Hurry!
[GERMÁN]
Get back in there now!
Now, on to find Mendoza.
[GERMÁN]
Damn.
And here I thought
this was going to be easy.
[gasps]
Good to see you again, Roberto.
What fun.
I guess neither one
of us is the same man
we were when
last we spoke, friend.
You have opted to
become a lunatic's hound.
[BERNARDO]
Very witty.
Finally, I can test
those blades of yours!
[GARM] They made
an oath long ago.
They smiled
in days past.
All that remains now
is dust and memory.