[ALFONSO] I have seen what
it is to fight Horrors, sir.
And I will do whatever I must
to take up arms against them.
Sir Rafael, please!
Mold me as you will!
[TRAVELER 5A] There she is,
gentlemen: the Mond River.
Cross that, and we'll
be in Santa Bard.
[metal clanging]
[JORDI grunting]
[SOLDIER 6A]
Pardon us!
We're soldiers from the castle,
sent here on urgent business.
From the castle?
Sergi must have come along.
Where's that son of mine?
We thought you would want to
have your son's sword, sir.
[JULIO, JORDI gasp]
[GERMÁN]
We've finally returned.
[LEÓN] Yes. To the land
that killed Mother.
That's right.
And the place where
your story began.
How can we best
infiltrate the castle?
What's the rush, León?
We've only been
here for a moment.
There's no shame in
catching a breath.
[LEÓN grunts]
You're kidding, right?
Now that we're finally
here, you just--
[GERMÁN]
Listen, son!
Who knows what all might
have changed in 17 years?
Anita and Carmen, for example.
Have they aged like fine wine?
And then there's
the matter of Paola.
I'm betting she's
really blossomed
in the time I've been away!
Hitting Mendoza on his home turf
means knowing the
lay of the land.
And when it comes to laying,
your old man practically
wrote the book on it!
Good luck with that.
I've got the money.
[gasps] Wait! I need
that! Oh, child...
I guess it's time
for us to go, Julio.
Please know that
you're always welcome,
if you happen to change
your mind later on.
Thanks a lot!
You take care.
I'm really gonna
miss you guys.
[knocking]
The others.
I don't think
they're coming back.
[JULIO gasps]
[SERGI]
Father... Father!
[gasps]
[SERGI]
Father!
Where are you? I'm here, Sergi!
[SERGI]
It hurts! Help me!
[gasps]
[SERGI]
Help me... live again!
[JORDI screams]
[GERMÁN]
That's quite a sword.
Please, forgive me, but we're
not selling anything right now.
Your wares aren't
what brought me here.
Huh?
Truthfully, I just
blew into Santa Bard.
I had a couple questions
about that castle up there
on the hill. I thought a
blacksmith's shop might be
a good place to
start asking them.
[JORDI]
The castle, huh?
You look like you can handle
yourself in a fight, sir.
Come to earn a spot in
the knighthood, is that it?
Me, a knight? Uh, maybe.
They were looking for
new blood for a while,
but I'm afraid that time
has come to an end.
Lemme at least buy
you a drink or two.
You came all this
way, after all.
Wait! I mean, are you all right?
Yeah! For some reason, my mood's
suddenly gotten a
whole lot brighter!
[JULIO]
Uh, Boss. Wait up!
[gasps]
I've been seeing
a lot of soldiers
around this area lately.
They're out patrolling
the streets, day and night!
[WOMAN 6B] Can't blame
them for being cautious.
Not after what happened
with the prince.
What if he marches back in at
the head of some foreign army?
[WOMAN 6C]
Is that why they've recruited
so many men as of late?
God protect us all
if a war breaks out.
[BROTHEL MOTHER 6A]
You, there!
The young man with
the stern face!
[gasps]
This bleu cheese from the town
of Berlu is like nothing
you've ever tasted before!
Here, why don't you give it
a try, it's on the house!
I'm fine. Thank you, though.
--[gasps]
--[water splashes]
[gasps]
Never mind the cheese, then.
Not if you've found something
else that's more to your liking.
A roll in the hay is sure
to put a smile on
that face of yours.
And that one there has
never had the pleasure.
A handsome guy like you?
She might let you do it twice.
Look, I'm sorry, but I really
didn't come here for that.
Could be you followed
your dowsing rod, then?
--[LEÓN] Hey! Unhand me!
--Ain't no shame in it!
[EMA] León, you silly goose!
You mustn't wander off!
Ema? What the hell
are you doing here?
Come on, let's away.
Hold on! Where're we going?
Some place the cheese
won't give you a rash.
Give me what?
Dammit all. We almost
had him, too!
He's got one that's
been around the block,
from the looks of her.
If I knew he was partial
to older women,
I'd a broadsided him
with these widow makers!
Ya mighta killed him!
[BOTH laugh]
[LEÓN]
Hey! Wouldja let go?
I could've handed that!
You didn't need to butt in!
[EMA]
Oh, really?
So you would've ravished her,
had I not dragged you away?
[LEÓN growls]
Don't be a fool!
I would never do
something like that!
Not 'til, you know,
there's a girl.
And we get there.
In our own time.
[gasps] You mean you've
never bedded a girl?
Not once?
You really are a chico.
Not that there's anything
wrong with that!
[LEÓN]
I don't need your pity!
I'm not like my old man,
all right? Or you.
[EMA]
Yes, I get that.
We're much less
prone to yelling.
[LEÓN]
Shut your mouth!
It's none of your
business what I do!
[EMA sighs]
Well.
I suppose you don't know
about any new Horrors
showing up around here, do you?
No, why should I?
You don't even
have sense enough
to be ashamed of that.
[EMA]
Listen, chico, and listen well.
Anger isn't a virtue.
All it does is blind
you to the things
you're too enraged to see.
What're you trying to say?
[EMA] You need to
become a man, León.
And quickly. In every
sense of the word!
[JORDI laughs]
[SHOPKEEPER 6A]
Drink up, Jordi!
This round is on the house!
Aw, you're a real prince!
Folks around here hold
you in high regard.
It's hard not to like the man!
Not only is he one of the finest
blacksmiths I've laid eyes on,
but the work he did while
on the citizen's council
has done a lot of good
for us common people.
Well, then!
Sounds like he had
that beer coming!
[GERMÁN, SHOPKEEPER 6A laugh]
[SHOPKEEPER 6A]
Ya got that right!
[GERMÁN] Do you mind if I
ask about the Knighthood?
I forgot!
That's what we were
talking about before!
It's old enough news
in these parts,
but the knight who'd been
heading up the King's army
lost his life in some
sort of accident.
The man's body wasn't even
cold when a new fellow
showed up to fill the vacancy.
[JORDI] Armor dark as the abyss.
Cut a dire figure, he did.
Folks took to calling
him the Black Knight.
[GERMÁN]
Naturally.
[JORDI]
He founded a new military order,
deep within the castle's walls.
They call themselves the
Brotherhood of the Black.
Between their fighting prowess
and their dark armor,
their foes are right
to be terrified.
They sound like a force
to be reckoned with.
Their numbers were low, so in
a move to fill their ranks,
they cast their nets far and
wide in the hunt for able men.
[GERMÁN]
Even the peasantry?
[JORDI]
Even us.
They took in hopefuls from
all over the kingdom,
money and birth be damned.
They said that if you passed
the real combat test
at the end, you could
even be knighted.
Hell of an incentive,
wouldn't you agree?
[GERMÁN] Hm. So they'd
fight to the death?
That they would, my friend.
I know better than most,
for I have got a personal
connection to it.
[thud]
[JULIO pants]
Sergi, my son.
Took everything
they threw at him,
and passed with flying colors.
Call it empty bragging,
but I'm proud as hell
of that boy.
Would've been easier
just to learn my craft
and live a simple life,
but he wanted to do
right by the kingdom.
Like father like son, I'd bet.
Kind of you to say that.
[groans]
What's the matter?
Damn head. Guess I
drank too much.
Looks like I'll have to
call it a night. Sorry.
Find me tomorrow if you
wanna talk some more.
Uh, all right. Get home safe.
[JORDI grunts]
[GERMÁN]
Hm...
[door clicks]
[JORDI panting]
Hey.
[SOLDIERS gasp]
You're two of those
knights from the castle.
[panting]
You better tell me
where my son Sergi is.
I've never heard of him.
I'm sorry, but--
My boy is one of your
comrades-in-arms.
How could you not know him?
Not a single one of us
goes by that name!
[panting] What kind of fool
do you take me for?
You're lying to me!
Liars, all of you!
--[HORROR JORDI roars]
--[SOLDIERS yelp]
[BUTCHER 6A]
You mangy little thief!
[VILLAGERS gasp]
I caught ya runnin' off
with my most expensive cut!
Give it here!
[pants]
[JULIO]
Leave him alone!
He's just a hungry little kid!
So what?
I don't care how small
of a brat he is!
That meat belongs to me!
Unless you're gonna pay
for it, you shut your mouth!
I would, but--
[LEÓN]
I'll pay for it.
[gasps]
Yeah? Big talk. Sure you will.
You think that'll cover it?
Huh? Uh-huh. I'd say
that's more than fair.
C'mon, don't worry about him.
[YOUNG THIEF whimpers]
[yelps]
[JULIO]
Um. 'Scuse me.
[LEÓN]
Really, it was nothing.
It was a lot more than
anybody else did!
[LEÓN] What's this about?
Do you know that boy?
No, I don't. I've never
met him before.
But until my boss helped me,
I used to be that boy.
My parents, they tossed
me away in the slums.
[JULIO gasps]
[JULIO groans]
[JORDI]
Hey, kid! You okay?
Hey! Let me know
you're all right!
Just hang in there!
[JORDI]
Hold your head up, Julio.
Even the king and his knights
use the swords we make.
Bloodline doesn't
matter in a smithy.
Only the sweat of your brow.
Long as you're willing to work,
you can forge yourself
into the man you wanna be.
Take those words close to ya.
Ho, lads! I wanna
tell you something!
This little ragamuffin needs
someone to raise him right,
and I'm the man for the job!
--Sergi!
--[SERGI] Huh?
[JORDI]
Meet your little brother!
Hey, Julio. Welcome
to the family!
Thanks to the Boss and Sergi,
the smithy felt like
my home in no time.
Watching you help that
little boy back there brought
all those memories
back up for me.
[LEÓN]
I paid for his food, that's all.
Well, either way,
I'm really glad
you stepped up to the occasion!
It must have been fate,
you passing by when you did!
[sighs]
What's he doing here?
Hm?
Glad you could join us
for dinner, freeloader.
Geez. Your timing's impeccable.
That bread looks pretty
tasty, hypocrite.
León is my guest, sir.
I invited him here.
What?
How the hell'd he charm
ya that quickly, kid?
There must be a much
nicer side of him
than the one he
shows me all the time!
Hard to tell which one
of you is the parent here.
You're a rogue, Germán.
Right down to your bones.
But you ended up with
a real good son.
Don't I know it?
It pains me how he doesn't
follow my example.
I'm sure he's a comfort
to you, morals and all.
Guess again!
His tongue is so sharp, I feel
I've been snake-bitten!
Just where do you get off
looking down on me?
Save the lecture for
yourself, whoremonger!
--[JORDI groans]
--Something wrong?
Just a little head pain.
Try not to get too angry.
You're lucky to
have one another.
[GERMÁN]
Yeah, you ingrate!
You should be thankful
for a father like me!
[LEÓN]
Why?
All you've ever done is
show me how not to act!
That's enough. Calm down.
All right! Gloves off!
If that stick went any
farther up your ass,
people would think
you're a tree!
[JORDI yells]
Get out! Both of you!
Do you mean it?
I must have a fever.
My head feels fit to burst.
I apologize for my words.
Please stay as long
as you'd like.
[door creaks]
It was boorish of us
to bicker like that.
Let's be on our way.
[JULIO]
Please, wait! Forgive him!
He didn't mean anything by it!
We were acting like
a pair of donkeys.
He was right to get angry.
[JULIO]
Mm...
What is it?
You can trust us, we're friends.
At the tavern.
Remember when the
Boss was telling you
about the knights at the castle?
Yes.
And he said his son
was among them.
[JULIO]
Big Brother Sergi isn't there.
Come again?
[JULIO] He didn't survive
the trial by combat.
[GERMÁN, LEÓN gasp]
They brought his
sword to the shop
so the Boss would have
something to remember him by.
Ever since that day,
he's been different.
He sent away the
other apprentices,
and the fire's gone dark.
When he looks at me,
it's like I'm a stranger!
I'm sure it sounds
foolish, but it's like
he's been possessed
by something!
I'm afraid all the time!
I keep thinking about it,
but I don't know what to do!
Please listen to me.
There's something
you need to hear.
Huh?
[door creaks]
No doubt about it.
There's a fiend on
the loose out there!
[SOLDIER 6D yelps]
[SOLDIER 6E screams]
I swear to God! Your son
is dead, all right?
He died right in front of me!
[HORROR JORDI]
He's not dead, but you are.
[whimpers]
[screams]
[HORROR JORDI]
Liars, every last one of you.
Give Sergi back to me.
[screams]
[JULIO] Please, Boss!
Sergi is gone, forever!
He's not coming back!
[HORROR JORDI]
Why would you lie to me, Julio?
After all I've done for you.
But it's true!
[GERMÁN]
León!
Leave this one to a father.
[HORROR JORDI grunts]
[GERMÁN]
That's a new one.
[HORROR JORDI grunts, groans]
You know I would've broken
that little boy in half!
[BOTH gasp]
[BOTH yelp]
[HORROR JORDI grunting]
[GERMÁN yells]
[HORROR JORDI groans]
[GERMÁN grunts]
Why'd he have to die?
He was a good man!
He saved me.
But when he needed saving,
I couldn't do anything for him!
I'm sorry, Boss!
[GERMÁN] You know, people are
pretty damn fragile, at heart.
Hit them in the wrong
spot, and it all comes
tumbling down in a
landslide of raw emotion.
The past is dead
and gone, Julio.
All you can do now is set
your gaze to the future.
I'm afraid. But I'll try.
[EMA] Hm... Well, Germán,
even a broken clock
is right twice a day.
[JULIO] I wonder if people
will ever respect me,
the way they did the Boss.
[LEÓN] "You can forge
yourself into the man
you want to be," remember?
[JULIO]
Words to live by.
[metal clangs]
[GERMÁN]
So, wherefore this tête-à-tête?
[EMA] You know how they've
been recruiting new knights?
Yes, the Brotherhood
of the Black.
Candidates kill each other
for the privilege of joining.
Uh-huh. What you might
not know is they take
the winners down underground
before the ceremony
to initiate them
as knights begins.
[GERMÁN]
What awaits them?
Painted ladies and
booze aplenty?
Not likely.
A chambermaid said
she heard screaming
as she passed by
the door one night.
It was a man's voice.
Oh, what did he say?
"Save me. Don't let that
demon take my body."
[GERMÁN] Either way, those
poor bastards are done for.
Perish in trial by combat,
or get devoured by a Horror.
What the hell is this?
[HORROR VOICE 6A]
If you want glory...
[HORROR VOICE 6B]
I'll let you feed...
[HORROR VOICE 6C] Honor and
admiration will be yours...
God above!
Save us!
[screaming]
It seems the creation
of our knights
continues apace.
[BERNARDO] Yes, but I'm
afraid one of your Horrors
has met with an abrupt end.
Was it a Makai Knight?
[BERNARDO]
Most likely, though I've reports
of a Makai Alchemist, as well.
[MENDOZA] Have the
Brotherhood of the Black
look into this matter
with all due haste.
[BERNARDO]
What? And deny myself?
I will kill them.
See that you do, then.
[chuckles]
[GARM] Where do the children
go when the harlequin
plays upon his pipe and
music's on the wind?
To paradise or perdition?