[HINA] Roll, roll, roll, roll,
roll, roll, roll, roll,
roll, roll, roll, roll.
There, nice and big.
[KENGO]
Cut it out!
We're not building snowmen!
But I can move
more snow this way.
[KENGO]
Well, you're not wrong.
I can't believe we're
lost in the mountains
and we have to build
an igloo to survive.
Snow big deal.
[TAKASHI] Are you really
making puns right now?
Wow, who peed in
your snowflakes?
[HITOMI]
Hina.
Takashi and Kengo are
worried, that's all.
This is a serious situation.
What's so bad about
being stuck out here?
[HITOMI]
Hmm...
--[stomach growls]
--Um, where should I begin?
Wrap it up, I'm hungry.
Uh... Well, for one thing,
we have nothing to eat.
[gasps]
[KENGO]
That should do it.
[HINA]
Kengo, Takashi.
[KENGO, TAKASHI]
Huh?
Being stranded in the
mountains is not good.
[BOTH]
Oh, really?
[HITOMI]
Let's wait here for help.
We should try to conserve
as much energy as possible.
It'll be hard, but we'll
get through this together!
[TAKASHI, KENGO]
Mm.
So what are we gonna do?
Feed me.
[TAKASHI] Wait! Me and
Mishima next to each other,
snuggling up against
the bitter cold?
Maybe things aren't that bad.
[KENGO] Man, it's freezing
up here at night!
Feed me.
It's all my fault.
I'm sorry I got carried away.
I don't understand.
What happens if no one
comes to rescue us?
We die.
[TAKASHI, KENGO gasp]
Are you sure?
[HINA]
Bathroom break.
That's our Hina.
Brings the whole room down
and then just leaves.
This is my fault, Takashi.
We only got into this mess
because I said I
knew a shortcut.
But we all went that way.
Don't blame yourself.
He's right.
Any one of us could have
made a mistake like that.
[KENGO gasps]
So I don't suck,
everybody sucks!
[TAKASHI] I'm pretty sure
you suck the most, dude.
[KENGO]
Hey.
Hina's been out
there for a while.
[HITOMI, TAKASHI gasp]
What was that noise?
--[thud]
--[ALL gasp]
[footsteps]
[HITOMI gasps]
There you are!
Hina. You had us all worried!
[HINA]
Guess what?
[ALL]
Huh?
There's a light back there.
[ALL gasp]
They might be out
there looking for us!
[KENGO]
I don't see anything.
You sure you saw something?
It was right there.
The cold's getting to you.
[HINA] Guys. I need to
tell you a big secret.
Dude. She's acting different.
I have super special
powers, okay?
I went outside to use them.
[ALL] The poor girl's
lost her damn mind.
[KENGO]
What's her problem?
[TAKASHI]
Is she hallucinating already?
[gasps]
[HITOMI]
Please forgive me, Hina.
[HINA]
Hm? Owwie!
Mishima! You're
taking it too far!
Yeah, you should
be slapping me!
--Huh?
--Uhh...
[HITOMI]
I need you to wake up, Hina!
Wake up?
[HITOMI] All we can do right now
is wait for help to find us.
If we waste all of our
energy wandering around,
we're gonna die out here.
[HITOMI gasps]
Hina!
[HITOMI]
Come on, guys!
We have to bring her
back--she'll freeze!
[TAKASHI]
Crap!
[KENGO]
Which way did she go?
[ALL pant]
Huh? What is this?
Are you kidding me?
[KENGO]
How is she floating?
You see? I said I had powers.
[TAKASHI]
No way.
[HITOMI]
This doesn't make sense!
Oh, I get it.
We must be the ones
who're hallucinating.
You really think so?
All I know is,
it started to get real weird
after Hina came back
from the bathroom.
Wait, are you trying to
say Hina never came back
from the bathroom at all?
Maybe she was never even here!
[TAKASHI]
I'm scared!
[HITOMI]
Check this out, guys.
[BOTH]
Huh?
I'm a believer now.
[TAKASHI, KENGO scream]
Wow, Hina, you're incredible!
I thought all you did was eat
and poop, but boy, was I wrong!
You're our ticket out of here!
You can use your powers tomorrow
to help someone find us!
You rock, Hina!
[KENGO]
Hm?
[HINA] I can't.
I'm too weak from hunger.
Why'd you have to build
up to it like that?
Good morning, Hina!
[HINA groans]
Where'd the boys go?
Don't mind them.
Can you use your powers?
Nope, still too weak.
That's too bad.
Come with me, then.
I have an idea.
Huh?
Where are we going? Tell me.
Hina. I need you to close
your eyes for a while, okay?
Huh?
If you do, then I promise
you'll get plenty to eat.
There's food here?
--[HITOMI] Ding ding!
--Come on in!
Welcome to Yukiyama Sushi Shop!
[HINA]
Mm?
Here we go. Let's
sit at this table.
[TAKASHI]
Have some tea.
So, what'll it be, Hina?
Uh, well...
How 'bout salmon roe?
Excellent choice, m'ladies!
And for today,
we even have it as a roll!
Order up!
One roll of salmon roe!
[HITOMI]
Say "ahh."
Like it?
[HINA]
It's really cold.
This is just snow.
That was our best
salmon roe! How dare you!
Sorry. Maybe it wasn't
defrosted all the way.
[HINA]
You guys are full of it.
Please, Chef! Make us a buttload
of salmon roe, on the double!
[KENGO]
Uh, okay!
Order up!
Oh, wow, Hina.
This salmon roe's awesome!
You should fill up on it
so you'll be strong enough
to use your powers!
[HITOMI whimpers]
[HITOMI]
I gave myself a headache.
[TAKASHI]
Uh, Mishima?
[KENGO]
You okay?
[HITOMI laughs] Yeah, I guess
I used too much wasabi.
[KENGO, TAKASHI]
Huh?
[HITOMI laughing]
[TAKASHI groans]
Salmon roe rolls don't even
come with wasabi!
See that, Hina?
She scarfed it right down!
Sorry. I didn't see it.
There's more!
Clean your plate, Hina!
Roll with it!
[HITOMI whimpering]
If I try hard enough,
then I think I can
get my strength back.
Over there! I see something!
Is it them? [gasps]
[ALL]
Help!
--Oh, thank goodness!
--Hurry! Help us!
We're down here!
Are they... having
some kind of festival?
[RESCUE B]
Hmm... Wait, I know.
[RESCUE A gasps]
[RESCUE B] They're
supposed to be the ginger
on the side of the plate!
[RESCUE A] Never mind that,
let's get down there!
[groans]
[NITTA]
You're awake.
[gasps] Hey, Nitta.
[NITTA]
You okay?
[HINA]
Mm-hmm.
Always somethin'.
When are you gonna give
my poor nerves a rest?
[HINA] I want some
real salmon roe, please.
Not the cold stuff.
What?
[NITTA]
I still don't get you, kid.
[NITTA sighs]
[NITTA]
Whatever you want.
All that matters to me
is that you're safe.
[sighs] Yeah.
[gasps]
I'll go do the dishes.
[ANZU]
Did you have a good trip?
We sure did. You should come
with us next time, Anzu!
Yeah!
Ahh!
[HINA yawns]
Hina. You shouldn't
sleep till noon
just because there's
no school today.
[HINA]
Feed me.
[PEDESTRIANS chattering]
[ATSUSHI]
Made it!
Man, it's been a crazy ride
since we met Hina
three years ago.
Not much longer, guys.
I'll find a way to make
Rockusion a reality,
just wait and see!
Booyah!
[MONK C]
Gather round!
Behold, as we
demonstrate for you
the ultimate in
qigong martial arts!
[ATSUSHI gasps]
Ha!
[CROWD applauds]
Signups are over here!
All right!
That's the kind of magic
I've been searching for!
It's the same mind
power Hina's got!
Hey, kid, wait up!
[MAO]
Huh?
[ATSUSHI]
Can I talk to you?
[MONK F] Hey! What do
you think you're doing?
The line is over there.
Whoa, dude.
Since when are monks
so hands-on, huh?
Let me go!
I gotta talk to that
girl right away, dammit!
Who is that?
Lady Mao.
Don't concern yourself with
people of no significance.
You are the crown jewel
of Superhuman Martial
Arts, after all.
Please, guys! Just a sec!
I'm a rock star, dammit! Owwie!
[MAO sighs] This place
has everything I need,
so I thought life would be easy.
But now it's kinda starting
to take a strange turn.
And as cute as I thought this
kung fu outfit was at first,
it's time for a wardrobe change.
Right, Hina? Anzu?
Clothes are clothes,
what's the difference?
Feed me.
It's been almost
three whole years.
Now if only I could
make it to Japan.
[gasps]
Wait, what about that guy?
[MONK G] Master, I think I heard
Lady Mao muttering something
to those strange
wooden dolls again.
Is that so?
Her behavior still hasn't
changed. The girl's disturbed.
That aside,
was there a Japanese man
at the demonstration today?
Yes.
[MONK MASTER]
Interesting.
Keep an eye on him for me.
Lady Mao is the backbone of
Superhuman Martial Arts.
This place cannot
afford to lose her.
Sir!
[MAO]
Here, Hina. Say "ahh"!
[ATSUSHI]
Hey, the magic girl!
Huh?
I'm Atsushi, famous rock star!
Uh, we're not that big
in China yet, but...
[MAO]
It's that guy again.
Wait, maybe you've heard
one of our songs online!
Here, let me sing
a few for you--
You really don't have to.
Oh, okay.
Anyway, my band, Central Park's
working on a new
genre called Rockusion
that combines rock
with stage magic.
We went to the U.S. to
learn how to do magic,
but all the tricks we saw there
were the cheap, fake kind.
That's when I came across
your video online and said,
"This is it!"
I thought maybe
if you can teach me
that martial arts
magic you do,
it'd be a perfect fit
for my new style!
[MAO] What is this
weirdo talking about?
He's some kind of crazy person!
I thought I could discuss
going to Japan with him,
but maybe I shouldn't be
talking to him at all!
Well, what's your take?
[ATSUSHI]
She talks to dolls?
This chick's got serious issues!
I guess being a qigong master
screws with your brain.
That's so punk rock!
--[clattering]
--[gasps]
[MAO] Um, I should probably
get going now. So--
Uh, wait, don't leave!
Even though she had
to quit the band,
I want to show Hina
that I can do this!
So please show me how, okay?
[MAO]
Hina?
[gasps]
[gasps] You mean
this girl, right?
[ATSUSHI]
Yeah, her!
Well, kinda, just
not made of wood.
--[MAO sobs]
--Uh--huh?
Finally... someone
gave me a clue.
Huh?
Okay. I'll teach you qigong.
Rock on!
And you will take me to Hina.
Sure. We still keep in touch!
[MONK G]
You're not going anywhere.
[BOTH gasp]
Lady Mao. We've come
to escort you home.
Uh--oh, okay.
But first, I need
to talk to this guy
about something really quick.
You mustn't.
Whoa. What's up?
[MAO] No. I finally got a lead
on Hina after all this time.
If I let Shinyhead take me back,
then I may never
get another chance!
Lady Mao!
Go!
[MAN]
Owwie!
[WOMAN]
[ATSUSHI]
What are we running away for?
Just go!
Stop them!
--[MONK E] Owwie!
--[MONKS gasp]
She just attacked
one of our own!
We didn't want to fight
with you, Lady Mao,
but you've left us
with no choice!
[MAO] There's only
one way out of this.
I'll just have to use my
Superhuman Martial Arts
against them!
[MONK C yells, gasps]
--[MAO grunts]
--[MONK C groans]
[ALL grunting]
[MAO grunts]
[MAO, MONK F grunt]
[MONK F gasps]
[yells]
She really is the world's
top practitioner of Naika-ken.
Care to surrender?
[gasps] I knew I should've
purchased a life-proof case!
Huh?
Luckily we all use the
Find your Friends app.
Uh-oh. That's a crowd!
[MAO] If I blow all
of them away at once,
they'll know I have superpowers.
What should I do?
I don't know what's going on,
but I'll try my best to help!
If you say so.
Uh--huh?
[ATSUSHI] I'm floating above the
ground! That feels familiar.
[ATSUSHI screams]
[ATSUSHI]
Oh yeah, I remember!
This is what it was like
when Hina used her magic!
[MONKS]
Owwie!
[MAO]
Oh, no! I'm sorry!
Booyah!
That's what I'm talkin' about!
You're scaring me.
--Enough.
--[MONK E gasps] Sir!
[MAO]
It's probably not a good idea
for me to throw the old man.
[MONK MASTER]
Explain yourself, young lady.
This guy's taking me to Japan.
Japan? Nonsense!
Master was the one who
discovered your talent
and brought you to live here!
If he hadn't pulled strings
to raise your status,
you'd still be homeless!
But my skills have brought
you more students.
I'm sure you're more than happy
to have their tuition money.
So I think that means
I've repaid my debt.
[BOTH]
Why you!
[MONK MASTER]
You two. Wait.
[MONK A, MONK B]
But!
We appeared on TV.
Now we have ten
branches nationwide.
That was all thanks to you.
Therefore, if you can pass the
Superhuman Martial Arts trial,
I will allow you to leave us.
[MONK B]
No! Not that!
[MONK A] But no one's ever
passed that test, Master!
--Silence.
--Don't do it!
[MONK A]
It's far too dangerous!
--[MONK MASTER] Silence.
--[MONK B] She'll be killed!
--Silence. Silence!
--[MONK A] Please don't, sir!
--[ATSUSHI gasps]
--Master, what is that?
[MONK MASTER]
Mao.
[MONK MASTER] Your task is to
destroy this giant metal man.
[ATSUSHI gasps]
Rest assured.
None of us question
your abilities
when it comes to Naika-ken.
[MONK A]
Owwie!
[ATSUSHI]
[ATSUSHI groans]
But when you are faced with
an enemy like this one,
Gaika-ken is the
only real option.
I suggest you train in
that for a little while
and then go to Japan.
Please--[gasps]
It can't be. She's doing it!
[ATSUSHI]
You sure about this?
That might be too metal!
[MAO]
I'm ready.
[ALL gasp]
[MAO grunts]
But how?
Those bars were spinning too
fast for the eye to follow!
[MAO]
Ha!
[ALL gasp]
[MONK MASTER]
Mao, you have my permission
to start your own
branches in Japan.
All you have to do is bring in
as many new pupils as possible.
[MAO]
I will, Master.
And your first
student's right here.
Great.
Thanks to you, I'll be able to
start a brand new life in Japan.
[ATSUSHI]
Finally!
I have everything I need
to create Rockusion!
[MAO]
Finally!
I can explain to Miss Ikaruga
that I lost my balls.
[MAO]
Off to Japan.
The real Hina and Anzu
are waiting for me.