[ANZU]
Owwie!
Jeez, dropping people on the
ground is a serious design flaw!
[BIKER]
Whoa, you got a death wish?
Move outta the street
before you get killed!
And put some
damn clothes on, too!
Hey! Are you listenin' to me?
Turn off that stupid thing.
It's way too loud.
[BIKER]
That's it, now you've done it!
Don't talk about
my baby that way!
[BIKERS] Owwie! Owwie! Owwie!
Owwie! Owwie! Owwie! Owwie!
Owwie! Owwie! Owwie!
Owwie! Owwie! Owwie.
[ANZU] I'm gonna
borrow these for a while.
[ANZU]
You can't hide from me, Hina.
[BIKER]
Owwie.
[SABU]
Did you hear the news, Boss?
Jashinryuu got their asses
handed to 'em last night!
I'm guessing a war broke
out between the scrubs?
No, and you're never gonna
believe what did happen.
[NITTA]
Hmm?
Some little girl
beat 'em all by herself.
I know, I thought it was a joke!
[NITTA] That sounds like
something she could do...
[NITTA]
...but I was with her all day.
Hmph.
Nah, one telekinetic
kid makes sense.
But two?
Now that's bordering
on ridiculous.
You think she's...?
Maybe.
[COOK]
Wait, Miss! You got money?
Money? What for?
[NITTA groans]
That's not good!
You're seriously
not gonna pay, huh?
I'm way too busy to deal
with a dine-and-dash, kid!
I don't have to
take this from you.
Hang on.
Please, let me take care of it.
Wow. That's nice.
Uh. Sure, okay.
[COOK]
Thanks.
What'd you pay that
girl's bill for, Boss?
I wouldn't have been
able to enjoy my ramen
with her causing
a big scene like that.
True.
[COOK]
Order up!
[SABU]
Aw yeah, come to Papa!
Hey.
Yes?
[NITTA]
You can have mine.
Wait, what?
[NITTA] Crap. I didn't think
this through all the way!
[GANG MEMBER A]
There she is! Get her!
We've been lookin' for you!
You pissed off the wrong
bikers last night, half-pint!
Yeah, and that's the
president's jacket!
So?
Give it back, right now!
[GANG MEMBER A]
Owwie!
[GANG MEMBER C]
[GANG MEMBER B]
Owwie!
[GANG MEMBER D]
[GANG MEMBER A, C]
Owwie!
[ANZU]
Hey.
[gasps]
Do you know someone named Hina?
[GANG MEMBER A]
Hina? Hell no!
She's some kinda witch!
Uh... Nitta. Welcome home.
[NITTA] Why am I surrounded
by creepy horror movie kids?
What did I do to deserve this?
Hey, I'm hungry. What's for--
Why are you smothering my face?
[NITTA]
I'm just mad you exist.
[SHOP CLERK]
Come back!
You really think
yelling "come back"
is gonna make me come back?
[SHOP CLERK pants]
She's way too fast!
[NITTA]
Dine-and-dash and shoplifting?
She's caused a lot of
trouble these past few days.
I know, that's why
I was hoping you could talk
to the family about her.
She's so quick to hide
we can't catch her.
[NITTA] Yeah. We need
to nip this one in the bud.
Tell the local bums
there's a reward for
helping us find this girl.
Got it.
[NITTA] It might take
one super-powered kid
to find another.
What if Hina had crash-landed
in the middle of the city,
instead of my apartment?
Feed me!
Sabu.
[SABU]
Hmm?
No need to
freak out or anything,
but I just realized
I'm a national hero.
You are?
[ANZU]
What to do.
Maybe I should hit up
one of those
"convenience store" places.
Gotta get my next meal
from somewhere.
Oh!
That's right!
I came here to look for Hina!
But right now,
all I'm trying to
do is stay alive.
[SABU]
Hey, Boss?
We found her.
Roger that.
I'll go talk to her.
You and the guys can fall back.
[NITTA]
Hina, you're coming with me.
[HINA]
Hmm?
Nice work, Yassan.
Here's your pay.
My god.
What kind of shady business
have I got myself into?
I just hand-delivered
a poor defenseless urchin girl
to a group of street thugs.
Wow, dude.
Sounds pretty dark
when you put it like that.
That's enough!
It's time to actually find her!
No matter how hungry I am,
I'll get my hands on that girl
if it takes me the whole day!
Hi, Anzu.
Huh? I was prepared to
search the whole city for you,
and you just walk
right up to me?
Eh, oh well.
Hina!
Get ready for a butt-kicking!
[NITTA groans]
How come?
[ANZU]
Orders from the top.
I have to dispose of you.
Now time to bring on the pain.
[NITTA]
Whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa!
Wait a sec!
Don't do it here,
you'll make a huge mess!
I've got a much better idea,
if you just hear me out!
[ANZU]
Step aside.
No, you have to listen,
or Hina's gonna run away!
Nuh-uh.
[NITTA]
Want some salmon roe?
I'll totally run.
All right, fine.
What's your brilliant idea?
[ANZU]
The "made you look" game?
[NITTA]
You play rock-paper-scissors.
Then whoever wins has to try
and get the other person
to turn their head
in a certain direction.
If they look,
they lose the game.
But if they keep their eyes
forward for ten seconds,
you play again.
It seems kinda stupid,
but it might be a better test
of strength than fighting.
You're on.
Whatever it takes
to defeat Hina.
Ow.
[NITTA]
Salmon roe.
I will end you.
You're gonna run away
with your tail between
your legs, aren't you?
I eat loser kids like
you for breakfast.
[ANZU] Oh, that's it,
you are dead meat!
Right!
It's Hina versus Anzu!
"Made you look" game!
Begin!
Heh! I've been looking
forward to fighting you
for a long time, Hina.
[ANZU]
Let's do this!
Rock, paper, scissors!
Look at the ground!
That's ten!
Ugh. You're pretty good.
[NITTA]
Okay, let's do round two.
[HINA, ANZU]
Rock, paper, scissors.
Look up!
[roars]
[NITTA]
Stop!
[NITTA laughs]
Ow, my sides!
[ANZU]
She won't budge!
But I'm using
every bit of my power!
[NITTA]
Time for round three, ladies!
[ANZU, HINA]
Rock, paper, scissors!
Look to your right.
My neck! It's broken!
[NITTA]
So, uh, that's game.
Will you leave her alone now?
[ANZU]
Hina.
I had no idea
you were that strong.
Your power really is terrifying.
Wow. You think so?
Damn.
You put up a
decent fight, though.
[ANZU] Would you
hold still for a second?
Ow!
[ANZU] I'm just gonna
tell them you're dead.
They'll probably buy it if
I show them some of your hair.
[HINA]
Anzu.
Do you wanna hang out
before you go home?
Huh?!
Why would I do that?
I came to fight you.
[HINA]
You know.
I've learned lots of new
things since I've been here.
[gasps]
Hina.
You've changed, huh?
Not too long ago, you didn't
even know how to talk!
[NITTA sighs]
This is my life now.
Who would've thought?
[ANZU]
I should head home.
[NITTA]
Take care.
[HINA]
Anzu.
I'll see you later.
You dummy.
You're supposed
to be dead, remember?
See you never.
Huh?! Hey, what gives?
It's busted.
So I don't have a way home?
I'm stuck here?
What should I do?
I can't go back to Hina's.
[ANZU sobs]
So, Utako, baby.
Let's go out sometime.
I know this great French place.
What? Are you serious?
Course I am.
I would never joke about us.
Aren't you booked?
I'd like to order the sweetest
cocktail on the menu, please.
[NITTA]
Ladies.
You're breaking my heart!
You used to try to get
my business all the time,
but I don't hear
from you anymore!
It's not just you, either.
My dating life's been
oddly quiet lately.
I mean...
Well...
Hmm?
There's a rumor going around.
Word has it,
you're trying to spend more
quality time with your daughter.
So you've sworn off
philandering forever!
Aww!
[NITTA]
What?
[shrieks]
[WOMAN A] Wow, and you
used to be such a player!
[WOMAN B]
They say there's no greater love
than father and daughter!
[WOMAN A] Yeah, I heard you
dropped a million spoiling her
at the department store
the other day, too!
[WOMAN B]
Daddy's little princess!
Welcome home, Nitta.
[NITTA]
It's because of her.
Is it almost dinner?
[NITTA]
This entire thing is her fault.
Her fault!
Here.
[gasps]
What is this?
[HINA]
It's not too bad.
[NITTA]
That's it!
I've made up my mind!
I won't let her ruin my life!
[HINA] I am gonna go out
there and philander my ass off!
Be home in a bit.
But it's nighttime.
Exactly.
[laughs]
All right, girls!
Time to drink
and party all night!
Ooh! Nitta!
Again?
[WOMAN B]
Oh my, you're such a gentleman!
[HINA]
Again.
[WOMAN B]
I can't believe you finally
asked me on a date, Nitta!
[NITTA laughs]
I'mma show you a good time!
I'm heading out.
[approaching footsteps]
Whoa.
What's wrong, kid?
I'll come with you.
Say what?
You've been going
out every night.
Take me, too.
[NITTA screams]
Damn. Brat's relentless.
[HITOMI]
You okay, Hina?
Nitta's acting funny lately.
By "Nitta,"
you mean your dad, right?
He's always leaving
me home by myself.
And he only lets me eat
canned mackerel for dinner.
Um. I'm sorry, Hina.
I wasn't trying to pry
into your home life!
I know!
[HITOMI]
You want to stalk your dad?
[HINA]
Yeah.
But why do you need me?
There's always more
than one person
when they do this on TV.
And that's not all.
This whole town
is covered with traps.
[HITOMI]
He's walking away!
Where'd she go?
[HINA] Now I see what
you mean by traps!
Looks like we lost him.
[HINA] I have a pretty good
guess where he's headed.
[HINA]
Utako.
Utako?
[HITOMI] The sign outside
says they're closed.
I'll go find her.
You stay here, Hitomi.
Huh? Hina, wait!
[TANAKA]
Utako! I'm ready to get drunk!
[laughs] I only had
five or six on the way!
[HITOMI]
Um, sorry, sir!
The bar's not open yet, so--
[TANAKA]
Who are you?
Did Utako quit?
You're young for a bartender!
Well, long as I get my drinks!
Um. I'm not a...
--Highball.
--But I can't--
What, you don't know
how to make a highball?
Well...
Don't worry, your ol' pal
Tanaka's here to teach ya!
But I... Okay.
[HINA]
So good.
[UTAKO]
Well, hello, Miss Hina!
[HINA]
Oh, Utako.
Why are you by yourself?
Here I am, Utako.
Did you miss me?
One highball.
Good job!
You're better than most
bartenders my age!
Uh, am I in the right place?
Nitta! Come on over here, buddy!
Oh, you're Hina's father, right?
Thank goodness!
I'm not anybody's father!
Got that?
[HITOMI]
Yikes! I'm sorry!
So whatcha drinkin'?
'Cause I'm buyin'!
[NITTA] You must've won at the
horse races today, eh, Tanaka?
Yup, practically
robbed the place.
[NITTA]
All right. Martini, please.
[HITOMI]
Oh, no.
[UTAKO] Well, what do you
think would be fair, Hina?
[HINA]
He should be punished.
He's always out
having fun without me.
And I bet he's not eating
canned fish for supper.
[UTAKO] So you wish Nitta had
more time to play with you, huh?
[HINA]
Yeah.
If you want him
to change his ways,
you should say so.
[HINA]
You think he'll understand?
He'll never understand
if you don't.
Nitta's a strange guy.
He's always trying to get me
to go to dinner with him.
And sometimes, his enthusiasm
alone is almost enough
to make me give in.
[HINA]
I get it.
So he's trying hard, too.
[UTAKO chuckles]
Anyway, we should head back.
[NITTA]
I'm just trying so hard.
You know what I mean, Tanaka?
How come I can't catch a break?
I know what you mean.
[UTAKO]
Huh? We're open?
What can I get
started for you two?
A kid?
Utako!
This one's got potential!
She's been soaking up everything
I teach her like a sponge!
One daiquiri.
I tell you, sweetheart,
she was born to be a bartender!
She'll be runnin'
this place in ten years!
Interesting.
[HITOMI]
There goes my life.
[HINA]
Hey, Nitta.
Oh. Hello there, Hina.
What're you up to, Hina?
[HINA]
There's something important
I've been meaning to tell you.
What is it?
Would you please...
take me with you...
...to the gentlemen's club?
What'd you say?
How about that, Nitta!
We've got the world's
youngest bartender
and the world's
youngest nightclubber!
Come on, where's the harm?
I dunno. Should we?
Oh hell yeah!
Everybody!
Let's have some fun!
[ALL]
Yeah!
You come too, Utako!
[TANAKA] Yeah! You can
close up early, can't ya?
[BAR GOERS] Gentlemen's
club! Gentlemen's club!
Gentlemen's club! Gentlemen's
Gentlemen's club!
club! Gentlemen's club!
Oh... So this is it.
Nitta!
Get us a champagne tower!
What? It's not a
wedding reception.
[WOMAN A] I'm sorry, miss. We
don't offer that service here.
Aww.
All you do is stack a bunch
of glasses in a pyramid, right?
[NITTA]
Don't bother.
Just leave the hard work to me.
Yeah, I'm gonna need a champagne
tower service delivered, please.
And make it quick,
we're trying to party here!
[ALL]
Yay!
[UTAKO]
It's beautiful!
All right, Hina.
Levitate that champagne
bottle, would ya?
Huh?
Are you sure?
Why not?
It's just a magic trick!
[TANAKA luaghs]
These little girls
can do anything!
[BAR GOER A]
That's amazing!
[HITOMI]
I'm not sure why I had to come.
[cell phone ringing]
[HITOMI'S MOM]
What's going on?
[HITOMI]
Mom?
[HITOMI'S MOM]
Do you know what time it is?
Where are you?
[HITOMI]
I'm uh...
Well, I'm at a gentlemen's club.
[HITOMI'S MOM]
Oh, ha-ha, very funny.
Just get your butt home!
Be right there.
God.
I feel like death.
Damn, this is
the hangover from hell.
[NITTA]
This doesn't make it any better.
[HINA]
Hey, you're finally up.
That was fun.
Let's do that again.
That was, uh, like,
a one-time thing.
We're gonna have to live
cheap for the time being.
Uh-oh.
[NITTA]
Next time, "Hobo Life 101."