[ANZU giggles]
I think you need a smaller size.
Nope.
It fits perfect!
My clothes've always
been too big.
[MR. HAYASHI]
I think you're ready now, Anzu.
But before you start your shift,
there's one thing
you need to know.
Every customer's a god to us.
Huuuh?!
I mean, they're godlike,
is more like it.
Just be as polite as possible
when you're speaking
to them, okay?
You got it!
[MR. HAYASHI] You mean,
"Yes sir, I'll do that."
When we're working, you need to
speak formally with us as well.
[ANZU]
Yes, sir, I'll do that!
Honey?
Let her shadow you today.
Okay, I'll show you how
we greet our customers.
For now, follow me around
and see how I do things here.
So, I don't have to do anything?
[MRS. HAYASHI]
Learning is part of your job.
[ANZU]
Mm!
Uh! Yes, ma'am.
I'll do that!
[MRS. HAYASHI]
Welcome, sirs.
Thank you, please come again.
You don't have to sit
at attention, sweetheart.
[MRS. HAYASHI]
That's too relaxed.
Since there's nobody
here right now,
why don't you study the menu
and learn about the dishes?
Yes, ma'am, I'll do that.
[ANZU shrieks]
The twice-cooked pork
is 800 yen?
I could buy eight
cup ramens for that!
[MRS. HAYASHI]
I need a tissue!
Get one for me, too!
All right, time to see how well
you do greeting a real customer.
[ANZU]
Yes, sir!
[door opens]
Welcome to--
Hey. It's Anzu.
Nitta.
Why are you here?
To get some food, why else?
Don't forget. Formal.
Hello.
Are you gentlemen ready
to order something?
Ramen and fried rice, of course.
Twice-cooked pork for me.
[ANZU gasps]
Twice... Twice-cooked...
You must be an extremely
wealthy person, sir.
[NITTA]
Not sure how to take that.
Ramen bowl with fried rice
and twice-cooked pork.
[MR. HAYASHI]
Got it, and by the way.
If you know the customer,
then it's okay to speak
a little more casually.
Okay, so everybody is a
god except for this guy?
He's just a mere mortal?
Great customer service.
Wow.
Thanks for your patience.
What are you
doing waiting tables, huh?
Oh, I'm living with
the Hayashis now.
Huh?
Hey. That's good news!
[CUSTOMER]
Excuse me?
Huh? Yes, sir!
I guess she's working to
pay for her room and board.
Yeah.
Too bad Hina's not like that.
Huh?
Dammit.
Don't think about it!
This is great!
[NITTA]
Thanks for lunch.
You want to try
the cash register?
[ANZU]
Yes, ma'am!
Do it exactly the way I did.
[ANZU]
Right!
Huh?!
A whole 1500 yen, please!
[NITTA]
You'll probably figure out soon
that that's not as big
a deal as you think it is.
[SABU]
There's not that much in there.
[NITTA]
Enough to make her go catatonic.
Hey, Anzu.
Are you done
with the dishes yet?
Uh. Uh...
You can throw away
the chopsticks.
Huh? We're not gonna
wash and reuse 'em?
No, there's no need to.
Really?
But Shige, he told me
it was better not
to let them go to waste.
[MR. HAYASHI]
Oops.
Everyone you meet becomes
part of you in some way.
I was trying to help,
but I'll probably end up having
to take that back
before it's over.
Nice work today, Anzu.
Do you think this is
a good job for you?
Yeah! Sure!
Uh, I mean, I'll do my best!
Okay, you can stop
being formal now,
we're done for the day.
Bath's ready.
Go ahead and
get cleaned off, dear.
[ANZU
'Kay!
Does the shower work okay?
[ANZU]
Yup!
Oh!
The water's ice cold!
Yeah. What's wrong?
I always took my showers at the
park, so I'm pretty used to it.
Please use hot water, Anzu.
I insist!
Wow. I'm even allowed
to turn on the light
whenever I feel like it!
It didn't really hit me
when I first got here,
but I have my very own bedroom!
I live in a real house!
[laughs]
[ANZU]
Yassan. Shige. You guys.
I'll work hard,
so you'll be proud of me.
Question:
Name a type of pan that
isn't used for cooking food.
As many as you can.
The pans in sickbeds?
[NITTA] Nope. Not quite
what I'm looking for!
Pan flute, no wait, pan-ties!
[NITTA]
Good one!
[TEACHER A]
Nitta! Nitta!
Wake up right now!
You're always
sleeping in my class!
I have had enough of you!
If you're going to nap the whole
day away and flunk your exams,
then why do you even
bother coming to school
in the first place?
Are you listening to me, Nitta?
Seriously, are you?
I can't tell with that
blank face of yours.
I don't enjoy scolding you,
you know that, right?
I'm doing it for your own good!
As any decent educator
knows, a student needs
a bit of tough love to prepare
them for the real world!
One day, you'll look
back on your time here...
[HITOMI]
Am I possessed?
[HINA]
Can't you give me some more?
There won't be
enough for the others.
[HINA]
You're a cheapskate.
You're selfish!
Nitta. School's boring.
Huh?
Well, you're the one
who wanted to go.
Sorry, but if you're
that bored with school,
you'll have to find a way
to make it interesting.
[MATSUTANI] We're choosing
candidates for student council
during homeroom today, so
speak up if you'd like to run.
You're dismissed.
[HITOMI]
Uh-oh, she's drooling again.
Hey, you should run
for student council.
You're smart.
Oh no, I could never win!
You'd be perfect though, Sayo.
Since you wear glasses!
[SAYO]
What's that supposed to mean?
What does a student council do?
[HITOMI]
Uh. Uh...
They set budgets for
the school sometimes,
and they come up with
new rules, stuff like that.
[SAYO]
Maybe in anime.
[KENGO]
It means you've got the power.
You're like the king!
[HINA]
Whoa.
They rule the school?
Yeah, and the student
council president
gets to boss them around!
Stop talking out yer butt.
[KENGO]
Oh, come on, it's just Hina.
The boss, huh?
[laughs] Sure is great
to be in a position of power!
I'm the boss!
I get to make the rules!
[GOOD GUY]
Dammit, I can't oppose this guy,
he's got too much authority!
[laughs]
--[BAD GUY] Yeart! Yeart! Yeart!
--[GOOD GUY] Owwie! Owwie!
[MATSUTANI]
Okay.
Who here would like
to run for student council?
Huh?
No.
Okay, then. Anybody else?
Anyone? Please?
Hina Nitta.
Are you insane?
Nitta has every right
to run if she wants,
I guess I can't stop her.
[HITOMI gasps]
What has gotten into you, Hina?
I'm gonna become
student council president,
so I can rule the school.
[HITOMI]
The president?
You just had to put those
ideas in her head, Kengo!
Sorry!
But, hey, I thought first years
could only campaign
to be members.
[SAYO]
Hang on.
I want to watch
this crash and burn.
[HITOMI]
Wow, Sayo.
[MATSUTANI]
Listen.
You'll have to give a speech at
the school assembly next week.
Can you handle that?
I got this.
[MATSUTANI]
In all my years of teaching,
I've never been more
scared by "I got this."
You have some bright
students in your class.
I hear one of them's running
for the student council!
[TEACHER]
He just blew me off.
What are you working on, Hina?
[HINA] All the candidates
have to give a speech.
Here's what I have so far.
Let's see!
[HINA] "I want to sleep
without getting scolded.
I want more for lunch.
The end."
[screams]
[HITOMI]
Hina.
You were supposed
to write a formal speech,
but this just looks like
a bulleted list of demands!
[NITTA] Running for
student council president?
[HINA]
Yeah.
Great.
Gimme one second.
There.
Sorry, guess
I was still half-asleep.
'Kay.
I'm listening.
Running where?
To be the
student council president.
So I wasn't dreaming after all.
First-year students can run
for president at your school?
Man, things have really
changed since my day.
I wrote a speech,
but someone told me it was bad.
Let me see, then.
Yeah, that's bad.
[HINA]
Help me.
You'll have to figure
this out yourself.
I'm busy.
[HINA] But, Nitta,
you're the one who told me
to find a way to make school
interesting, remember?
[NITTA]
So that's Hina's new strategy
for bugging the crap out of me.
Come on!
It's not like she actually
stands a chance of winning.
[BOSS]
Huh?
Hina's trying to make
something happen.
And look at you,
sittin' on your ass.
Now!
Support your little princess,
you deadbeat dad!
[BABA]
Here's a thought.
Why don't we get our company
lawyer to write her a speech?
--[NITTA] What?
--[BOSS] Hey, now!
That's what
I'm talking about, Baba!
Did one of you have a run-in
with the police or something?
No, no, it's far more
serious than that.
Oh. Dear!
I'll do what I can to help!
[BABA]
He actually called him.
[VICE PRINCIPAL] And now,
we'll hear the speeches
from our candidates
for the student council.
Hina Nitta from Class 1-3.
[TAKASHI]
Oh, man.
This is making me nervous.
Me too. Hina's bound
to screw this up somehow.
My name's Hina Nitta
from Class 1-3.
When I'm student
council president--
[VICE PRINCIPAL]
Just a minute!
First-year students can only
run for secretary or treasurer.
When I become
student council president...
[STUDENTS]
She ignored him!
...the first order of business
will be improvements
to our school lunches.
Some of you may know our
school has been ordering them
exclusively from Asaka Lunch
Center for the past 25 years.
However, the long-standing
contract that we,
as well as many neighboring
schools, have with Asaka
is not favorable in terms
of cost or food quality
and must be replaced
with something more
beneficial to students.
I propose choosing a supplier
through competitive bidding.
This will help us
to lower costs,
while at the same
time increasing...
Is she...
...making sense right now?
By enacting this change,
the result will be better
food safety as well as
better health and nutrition
all over campus.
Uh...
Take a deep breath
here and hold it.
[STUDENTS]
Huh?
Deep breath?
[HINA] Of course, once
the food quality has risen,
the student body's
daily need for naps
will also naturally increase.
[MATSUTANI]
Something's not right here.
[HINA] Raise arm here
for dramatic effect.
My next proposal,
is afternoon naps.
Did she really say
"afternoon naps"?
I'm more concerned
with the arm thing.
[HINA]
Please observe this data
on the benefits
of regular napping.
I believe these charts
speak for themselves.
[STUDENTS]
I don't think they do!
Thank you all for your time.
This is the conclusion
of my student council
candidate speech.
Bow to the audience.
It may have been
a bit unorthodox,
but I thought it was
an excellent speech.
Well, aside from the
fact that it grossly
overreaches the authority
of the student council.
[SAYO] We knew you
weren't going to be president,
but secretary's cool.
[HITOMI]
Hina, wait!
Huh? Something wrong?
I didn't get to
take over the school.
Probably for the best.
Anyway, what do you say we
go out for dinner somewhere?
Any special requests?
[HINA]
Salmon roe!
Really?
Hina hasn't shown up to a single
student council meeting?
[COUNCIL MEMBER A]
Nope.
The president's had enough
and wants me to drag
her there if I have to.
I know.
I'll bring you instead!
[COUNCIL MEMBER A]
Same difference.
[HITOMI]
Huh?
It's all done, President.
Perfect.
What's this?
[HITOMI] I thought it'd be
easier to read that way.
[HITOMI]
I need to go.
I'm supposed to open today.
I went ahead and
reorganized these, too.
[GOROU]
Huh.
That does make more sense.
[HITOMI]
Just let me leave.
Those forms for
the sports festival.
[HITOMI]
Already finished them.
Hurry up!
[GOROU]
I'm glad you came today.
I was getting worried.
Huh?
Good job, Nitta.
[HITOMI]
Mishima, actually.
I'd better get going.
[GOROU]
Wait a second!
Can you come to every meeting?
We need a secretary,
and Nitta's never gonna show.
Welcome to student council!
[COUNCIL MEMBERS] Welcome!
Welcome! Welcome! Welcome!
[NITTA] So, Utako,
when are we getting dinner?
Well...
I dunno, Nitta.
Work is pretty busy.
But the place is always empty,
so what's your next excuse?
How can you say that?
It may be empty, but it's mine,
and I have to watch over it!
[NITTA]
What are you, a gargoyle?
[NITTA sighs]
How do I get Utako
to go out with me?
Something wrong?
Nothing you
can help with, kiddo.
You'll feel better
if you talk to somebody.
Yeah. You might be right.
That's the last thing
I was expecting
to hear outta your mouth.
Got it from TV.
'Course you did.
I shoulda guessed that.
Okay, so here's my problem.
[NITTA] You're about to
ask a child for dating advice.
Dammit, me, where's your pride?
[HITOMI]
Wow, he really likes her!
I have seen him ask
her out a few times.
[HINA]
Yeah, she keeps saying no.
[HITOMI]
I see.
Hey! But if they
did get together.
I guess that would make Utako
your new mom, wouldn't it, Hina?
Huh? My mom?
Oh! I'm sorry!
I forgot, Hina's mom is, um...
A mom. Nitta has one.
[HITOMI]
That's right!
So what's the fastest
way for me to get them together?
Uh...
I don't think I'm the
best person to answer that.
I'm only a
middle school student.
I don't know the first thing
about getting a boyfriend!
I wonder what
having a mom is like.
[HITOMI]
Poor Hina!
She never knew
her mother at all!
[NITTA]
God, why?
[HINA]
What?
Look, I know I can't
bring your mother back
from the dead
or anything, but...
...I swear!
I'll help you somehow!
Don't worry!
[HINA]
Thanks, I guess.
[HITOMI]
Here we go, Hina.
Just brag about Nitta
as much as you can
and casually mention
them going on a date.
Got it?
[HINA]
Yup.
Oh, hey.
You brought Hina with you.
Nitta wants you to
go on a date with him.
[HITOMI] What part of "casual"
did she not understand?
That's classy.
I rejected him too many times,
so he gets his daughter
to come manipulate me.
[HITOMI]
Uh-oh.
That made her impression
of him even worse!
That's not it at all!
Hina just saw the
chemistry between you two--
Sure.
Yeah, you're right.
It's Hina.
Hurry! Say something
positive about Nitta!
Nitta's really cool.
He buys me food and
presents whenever I want.
[HITOMI]
That just means he's convenient!
Come on,
can't you at least go on
one little date with him?
It won't be that bad!
It's not like it's gonna
make any difference
if you're not at the bar!
[UTAKO]
Fine, then.
Huh?
[UTAKO]
I'll go. Are you happy now?
[TV HOSTS]
Stepmothers are fun!
[HINA]
Stepmother.
Nitta and Mika had black hair?
Hey, I'm back.
What's up?
I'm trying to
learn about mothers.
What for?
'Cause Utako's gonna be my mom.
[NITTA]
That's way too fast!
You really got me a date?
[HINA]
Mm-hm.
She's not messin' around!
Then again,
I have been pretty vocal
about the whole thing recently.
And here I thought having a kid
would lose me points
with the ladies.
She's just the
secret weapon I need!
What a smart girl!
Good job, Hina!
[NITTA laughs]
[HINA]
Owwie!
It's almost time for your date.
Yeah. But I can't
just ditch you.
It's my fault your leg got
busted up in the first place.
She can wait.
I can't go out and have fun, not
if you're stuck in the hospital.
[HINA]
It's okay.
I really want to
have my own mom.
[NITTA]
Hina.
[HINA]
Go, Nitta.
Huh? How can I say no?
All right, then.
When I come back,
you'll have a mommy!
Now you've got me
hoping for it too, kid.
You've seen my tears, Hina,
but don't show me yours yet!
Not till you get
to meet your mom.
Because then,
they'll be tears of joy.
I promise you, Hina.
Even though I'm
just a lowly yakuza,
the three of us are gonna
have a warm and happy home,
where we smile and laugh and
have fun together all the time!
Hang on, Hina.
I'll show you that I,
Yoshifumi Nitta,
can be the perfect family man!
[HITOMI]
What? You turned him down?
[UTAKO]
I had to.
Hina's completely
attached to him,
and Nitta couldn't stop talking
about her all day today.
I just don't know
if there's enough room
in there for me, you know?
So I told him I'm not
into sad, single dads.
You said that?
[UTAKO]
Why not?
Don't you think I should
be straightforward?
[HITOMI] That goes a little
beyond straightforward.
Yikes.
[NITTA]
Hina! Mommy's here!
Come on, hun.
Smile for me!
Er, please?
Just a little smile?
[HITOMI] Next time,
"And It's the Same Old Hina."