That? I lost it a long time ago.
[IKARUGA]
Damn it.
I'll have to get a
replacement orb delivered.
I should probably try
calling Mao first.
She's shy, but she'll get
the job done, at least.
Boom.
[MAO]
Owwie!
[MAO groans]
Huh? Am I in... Japan?
[MAO]
Oh, no.
I'm in big trouble!
How could I have
lost both of them?
I've been looking
for them for ten days.
I can't find the orbs
or Miss Ikaruga!
This is bad.
[MAO] I failed my mission
before it even started!
What am I supposed to do now?
[stomach growls]
I'm so lonely.
I thought I would get a chance
to see Hina and Anzu here.
Why did I have to end up
in such a terrible situation?
[MAO]
I don't like being alone.
[thud]
[MAO]
Ah!
[MAO giggles]
[MAO]
It's Anzu and Hina!
But they're not
really doing anything.
Wait, I know!
Jeez, Mao! Get over it, already!
Things aren't that bad!
Feed me.
It's kinda the same.
I messed up my assignment.
And now I don't know what
my next move should be.
Don't blame yourself!
It's Miss Ikaruga's fault
for sending you to this place!
You're stuck on
a deserted island!
What does she expect?
Feed me.
Heh. That's true.
Yeah, she's always
bossing us around!
Why don't we just hang out
here for a little while?
It'll be like, y'know,
a vacation or whatever!
A vacation?
Yeah, that sounds perfect!
Feed me.
Jeez, Hina! Is that
all you think about?
[giggles]
[MAO]
I'm still smarter than you.
What?!
[MAO laughs]
[MAO humming]
Check out my dress!
Do you like it?
As long as you have
something to wear,
who cares what it looks like?
Feed me.
You guys don't care about
fashion at all, do you?
Anyway, let's go!
[MAO]
Where are you taking us, Mao?
We can't have a vacation
without a cottage, right?
[MAO]
Hey, that's not half bad!
Feed me.
Don't you have more of that
jelly you're always eating?
I'm tired of it.
[MAO giggles]
Okay, I'll make lunch, then!
[MAO]
Eat up, Hina!
Nom.
No fair! Hina,
let me have some, too!
Don't worry, Anzu,
there's some for everyone!
Uh, I didn't say that
'cause I want some.
I'm just being polite
'cause you cooked it!
[MAO giggles]
[MAO]
Hope you like it.
[MAO chewing]
Splish splash, Anzu!
[MAO giggles]
Catch me if you can, guys!
[MAO giggling]
Wow, you're really good
at this game, aren't you?
[MAO laughing]
[MAO]
That's so cool!
[MAO laughing]
[MAO]
Is everything okay?
You seem kinda sad lately.
We call it a vacation, but it's
really just surviving, isn't it?
What do you mean?
It's a time to
relax and have fun!
Right, Hina?
Feed me.
Yeah, but...
...I can't stay here by
myself forever, can I?
You're not by yourself.
You have us.
So...
[MAO sobs]
It's okay.
You're never really alone!
[screaming]
[sobs] You guys aren't real!
You're not even close
to being Hina and Anzu!
You're just coconuts!
Feed me.
I should be... with people.
[SABU] Naito, huh? People
say he's the kind of guy
you don't wanna
mess around with.
[NITTA]
Huh? Oh, yeah.
He used to be to me
what I am to you.
Last time he was
sent to the slammer,
it's 'cause he used a sword to
fight off four guys with guns.
You don't get a nickname
like Naito the Slayer
for nothin', I guess.
See this scar?
[NAITO]
Ya dumbass!
[NITTA]
I got it a long time ago
when he smacked me
with an ashtray
because I forgot to
light his cigarette.
He sounds like a
villain in a B-movie.
Do not get on his bad side.
No prob.
--[door opens]
--[BOTH gasp]
[door closes]
Hey, Boss.
It's good to see you again.
It's been a long time, Nitta.
--Yeah.
--Uh, here!
Where's the president?
Take me there.
Rumor is he's been in a coma.
[BABA] So, you know
the prez is retiring.
[NITTA]
Yeah.
But then, as luck would
have it, the old dinosaur
went unconscious before he
could name a successor.
Yeah.
President! What's wrong?
I told him he smelled
weird and he freaked out.
Don't say stuff like
that to old people!
[NITTA] If he doesn't
come out of this coma,
I'll have a murderer
on my hands.
[BABA]
I'm next in line, of course,
but I can't move forward without
the support of the organization.
Heh. I know I've made you do
a little bit of dirty work
here and there in the past...
Yeah.
[NITTA]
You told me to kill a man.
But you should know,
I did all those things
for your own good.
What kind of president wouldn't
want one of his weaker guys
to grow a pair?
[NITTA] Gettin' ahead
of ourselves, are we?
Either way...
[NITTA]
Okay, Lieutenant.
If you need support,
I'll get it for ya.
[BABA]
You mean it?
I'll do everything in my power
to make sure you become
the next president.
[BABA]
Nitta.
[gasps]
You got the biggest,
hairiest balls I know.
[NITTA]
Uh, thank you?
First thing I need to do
is have a talk with Naito.
[NITTA] If I get his vote,
everyone else'll follow.
So what's your take on it?
Do you want Lieutenant
Baba to be in charge?
No.
You have to ask?
What makes you think I want
to give up this promotion
and let myself be cast to
the side, just like that?
I did time for these guys!
Nitta.
I can count on you to
support me, can't I?
I mean, maybe.
It's hard to give
a straight answer
when you're holding
that ashtray.
Come on now, don't be afraid
of this little old thing!
Look, Boss. [grunts]
I understand how you
must feel and everything,
but maybe you can
let this one go?
What? How dare you!
[BOTH grunt]
[NITTA] If the old man wakes
up to all this infighting,
I won't be able to show
my face here ever again.
I mean, this is the yakuza.
I might not have a face left!
That's enough--
[NITTA] Please, give your
support to the lieutenant,
so the president
can die in peace!
[NAITO laughs]
You know what, you're right.
[gasps]
[NAITO] I've been acting like
a selfish kid about this,
haven't I?
Naito.
Good job!
You've become a real
stand-up mobster! [laughs]
Thanks a lot!
[NAITO]
You know, Nitta.
You're not that terrible!
[NITTA] What is it with these
guys and their non-compliments?
[NAITO]
I just heard from Sabu.
He says the president
woke up from his coma.
[NITTA] Sir, you need
to pick a successor.
Yeah, never know which hospital
trip might be my last one.
It's better if I retire while
I'm young and limber, after all.
So, I assume the lieutenant
gets your spot, right?
[HINA]
Nitta.
What's a successor?
Does he get everybody's money?
Be quiet!
That's not quite it, little one.
This is a grown-up conversation!
[NITTA] He's acting like
she's his grandkid.
[HINA] I'm trying to make up
for saying you were stinky.
Don't worry, kid, I sprayed
myself down with Fasleeze!
[NITTA]
Ugh.
A successor is a guy who's
gonna take over my job
so I can be a full-time peepaw.
Ohh.
I want Nitta to do it, then.
[BOSS]
Why's that?
Nitta's a dad and an old man,
so we should consolidate
him. It's confusing.
What does that mean, exactly?
Just a minute.
Let me think.
Just for you, Hina,
I'll let Nitta do it.
[NITTA]
Cut it out, gramps!
You say that like
you're buyin' her candy!
[SABU]
No way. I gotta tell him!
This ain't gonna work!
[OTHERS]
Huh?
I've been begging
the whole group
to support the lieutenant
becoming the president.
Ya can't let this
organization go to the dogs
just to make Hina happy!
Uh, you're right. Sorry, Nitta.
Let's make Lieutenant Baba
the next president, okay?
[NITTA]
Glad you see it my way.
[SABU]
Oh, man.
He's gonna kill me if I
say it was a false alarm!
[SABU]
Maybe I'll say, "Oh, sorry,
I went to the
bathroom to text you
and didn't hear the end
of the conversation!"
That's still bad.
[NAITO]
Dammit! How did this happen?
Sabu says Nitta used his
daughter to get the old man
to make a verbal promise.
The guy does treat that little
girl like his own grandkid,
so I shouldn't be surprised.
[NAITO] How can you
be so calm about this?
That rat just cheated
the both of us
out of becoming the successor!
Forget what I said.
He is that terrible and I'm
gonna tear him a new one!
[glass shatters]
[BABA]
Calling me calm?
I didn't realize you were
such a jokester, Naito.
Heh. Well, now.
You look meaner than you did
during that feud ten years back.
I am a yakuza.
Backstabbers have to
pay with their lives.
That's my policy.
[NITTA groans]
So you're finally awake.
[gasps] What the hell?
I'm sure you know.
Your little scheme just
blew up in your face, Nitta.
Nothin' like good
old-fashioned payback.
Time to swim with
the fishes, traitor.
[NITTA gasps]
Uh, please tell me you know
what this is all about!
[SABU]
Um, nope.
[gasps]
[NAITO]
Whoa, whoa, you better not speak
without raisin' your hand first.
[NITTA]
I'm encased in concrete!
[NAITO]
Go ahead, pal,
I'm sure you wanna give him a
piece of your mind, don't you?
Hi, Nitta.
It was--I mean, um--
[NAITO] Huh? Disgusting!
Where's your pride?
Can someone fill me in here?
[BABA] I thought
I could trust you, Nitta.
I really did.
But no.
You had to use your rugrat
to con the old man
into letting you be
the new president.
Huh? Wait, I can explain that!
It's true, he did offer it to me
first because Hina won him over,
but I talked him
out of it, I swear it.
He said he wants you to
be the successor, not me!
But still, I've done such
a good job for the family.
It would've been nice
to be considered.
[NAITO sighs]
You're pathetic, Nitta.
You've been pullin' some
dirty tricks to get your way.
At least die with dignity.
This is it. I'm done for.
[BOSS]
Not so fast!
[HENCHMEN gasp]
What's goin' on here?
[BABA] I'm sorry you
have to watch, but...
...Nitta needs to
learn a lesson!
And since his death will
leave the position open,
I'll be glad to step in--
Now wait just a minute!
I only said that on a whim
and Nitta wouldn't have it!
Said to pick you!
[OTHERS]
Huh?
He's not lyin'?
Sabu. Explain yourself.
Seriously, guys, I don't know!
I just heard that Nitta was
gonna maybe take the job,
so I left the room
immediately to tell you!
Not again.
Well, in that case...
Uh, old man... is that
really what happened?
[BOSS]
Of course it is!
Unlike some of ya,
Nitta has the organization's
best interest at heart!
[BABA]
Guess we were wrong, Nitta.
Sorry about that.
Won't happen again.
[BABA]
Hey, I know!
How's this? You can take
my spot after I move up!
Zenba, I know you're
second lieutenant and all,
but you don't mind, do ya?
Uh, well--
Perfect! Look at that, Nitta!
Your career's really
takin' off, huh?
All right! Let's all give a
cheer for our new lieutenant!
It's an historic day!
[BABA]
Good idea!
[NAITO]
Here we go!
[BOTH]
Lieutenant! Lieutenant!
[ALL] Lieutenant!
Thanks. Now get me
the hell outta here.
[HITOMI]
A promotion is like an upgrade!
Like, when people
buy nice drinks?
Uh--yeah, maybe!
So he tastes better now?
Uh...
Hey, you should throw
him a promotion party!
I bet that'd make
him super happy!
[UTAKO]
That's not a bad idea!
Nitta's generous. He'd probably
give you something back, too!
You make me so sad.
I see. Both good points.
[MATSUTANI]
No way, that's not Hina Nitta.
It's just a part-time worker
who happens to look
exactly like her. Yeah!
Okay, a martini, please!
I need help.
I don't know how
to throw a party.
[phone chimes]
[VO] It depends on what you're
celebrating and who it's for.
We can't give you any advice
until you write that
in your question.
You could try asking
your acquaintances, too.
Hope that helps!
Wow. Technology's great.
[HITOMI]
Hmm. What about cake?
That's a birthday thing.
I'd print up a fancy portrait
of him and frame it!
That'd be a weird party.
Then what's your idea, Aizawa?
Uh--let's see.
Maybe some nice flowers?
[gasps] What, I don't
look like a flower person?
You can't celebrate
without drinking!
I say you get 'im some booze.
[HINA]
But you're always drinking.
'Cause I'm celebrating!
This life is a gift.
Every day I drink
a toast to being born.
Well, if it was my party,
I would want some
of my favorite food!
Make it a surprise.
Think of something that'll
totally blow him away.
Huh. That sounds tricky.
I'm more confused
than when I started.
[ANZU] I see! That's why
you came to me for help!
[HINA]
Nah, just food.
[ANZU]
Is that all you think about?!
I want to do something
really awesome, though.
Awesome. Awesome. Awesome...
I'll just do everything.
[NITTA]
I'm headin' out.
[HINA] Call me on the
intercom when you get back.
What for?
So I'll be ready.
Nothing you say
ever makes sense.
Explain.
To celebrate your promotion.
[NITTA gasps]
Hey!
Check.
[NITTA]
Should I be scared?
[HINA]
Check.
Now I just need to get
a few things from town.
[HINA]
Check.
Yeah, I can't sell to a minor.
Check. Heh.
[HINA]
I bought too many flowers.
[gasps]
I have some bottles.
[HINA]
I'm sure that's close enough.
[HINA humming]
Perfect.
[HINA]
Check.
What's Nitta's favorite food?
Everybody likes salmon roe.
I don't want to give
him too much, though.
There.
All done.
Never thought she'd do
somethin' special for me.
Man, I owe her big time.
Especially after that.
Hope she likes melon.
[intercom rings]
[HINA]
Uh-huh.
[NITTA]
I'm comin' up.
[HINA]
Got it.
Can I come in?
Can't wait to see
what you planned!
[clears throat]
Hey.
[NITTA gasps]
[NITTA] I just walked
into my own funeral!
What is all this crap?
That's the kind
of messed-up stuff
the bullies did in grade school.
What the--a candle in salt?
Salmon roe prayer beads?
[NITTA]
Is that the coffin?
[NITTA gasps]
[NITTA]
More importantly, where's Hina?
[gasps]
[NITTA]
U-Uh...
[HINA]
Aww...
Congrats on becoming lieutenant.
Thanks, kiddo.
[ANZU] Next time,
"Like a River Stream."