[NITTA]
I'm home.
[HINA]
Hello?
Yes. Yes.
[NITTA] Whoever it is,
we don't want any.
Wow. Are you really Nitta's mom?
Mm-hmm. Yeah, we live together.
[HINA]
Owwie!
Hiya, Mom--
[NITTA'S MOM]
Yoshifumi!
Who was that
young lady just now?
Young lady? That's weird.
Are you sure it wasn't a ghost?
[NITTA'S MOM]
Don't lie to your mother!
[HINA]
I'm telling your mom on you.
What're we doing?
[NITTA]
Praying.
My old man's dead, so I
check in with him sometimes.
The old man isn't dead.
I saw him.
[NITTA]
Not him, my actual dad.
I should say hi
to my family, too.
Are you up for that?
I got this.
I won't mess up!
That's promising.
Hina, this is my mom
and my little sister Mika.
Say hello.
[HINA]
My name's Hina Adachi.
I'm 13 years old.
My dad's in prison, and I don't
have any other family,
so I'm staying
with Nitta now.
Nitta always treats
me really nicely, though.
So my life is super fun.
Oh. Nice to meet you.
So, how long have
you and my brother
been living together, Hina?
[NITTA]
Uh. Hang on!
Let's direct the questions
about Hina to me.
Are you her boss?
You don't have relatives
on your mother's side?
Hello.
I'm Hina Adachi, age 13.
What, are you a frickin' robot?
C'mere.
I'll come up with the story.
You can just wait in the yard.
[HINA]
I did what we practiced.
But you suck at improvising.
It's easier to say
I'm taking care of you
and leave it at that.
Things'll get complicated
if we tell the truth.
Okay, I'll do my best.
Good. Do your
best outside, then.
[NITTA'S MOM]
That really happened to her?
[NITTA]
Yeah.
They went out to dinner,
and there was a big fight.
Her mom got shot.
Then, her father killed
two other people during
all the confusion.
He was like a brother to me.
I couldn't turn
my back on his kid.
That's why I took her in.
So Hina didn't
get injured at all?
Nope, she just ate
her chili shrimp.
Ah! Chili shrimp?
Seconds, please.
[NITTA]
That's right.
She was so traumatized
the shrimp is the only
thing she remembers!
[NITTA'S MOM]
That poor child!
[NITTA] When Hina
first moved in with me,
I couldn't get a
word out of her.
But now, after all
she's been through,
she's finally
beginning to speak!
Wait.
Wasn't she talking about
having a fun life though?
Uh, that's because...
...she's always trying
to keep a smile on her face,
so I won't worry.
She's so strong!
[NITTA] That's why it's better
not to ask about her past.
[NITTA laughs]
Chili shrimp, that's rich!
Oh man. I'm really good.
Maybe I oughtta be an actor!
[NITTA'S MOM] We should probably
start making dinner, Yoshifumi.
[NITTA]
Sure, sounds good.
It'd be nice if you would cook.
Yeah, cook!
But I'm the guest.
I assumed you'd do it
since you were coming by.
Why else would I have spent the
entire day chuggin' these beers?
[NITTA] That logic doesn't even
make sense to a drunk person.
Fine, if it's that
important to you,
then I guess I can
make us something.
Give me about three minutes
to boil the water.
[NITTA'S MOM]
Oh, it takes you three minutes?
I can do it in two.
[MIKA]
Nice one, Mom!
Yeah, on second thought,
I'll make dinner.
[MIKA] First year
of middle school, huh?
I bet that's fun.
[HINA]
Nah, I sleep all day.
I do like lunch, though.
[NITTA]
Dammit.
School's expensive, at least
pretend like you're learning!
[laughs]
I bet you're not doing
your homework, either, are ya?
[HINA]
Ah! That's right.
I have homework.
[NITTA]
She bothered to bring it home?
I've never seen her do homework.
Why start now?
Then again, if she's working
on that, she won't have to talk.
Good job, Hina!
Keep it up!
[MIKA]
Let's see.
What've we got?
Don't forget to write your name.
[HINA]
Oh yeah.
Uh!
[MIKA]
Hina Nitta?
[NITTA gasps]
Oh! Uh, yeah, about that!
Hold that thought.
We cleared it with the school!
They said it's better
if she uses my last name,
so the other kids
won't pick on her!
Heheh.
'Kay.
And Hina doesn't mind
them calling her Nitta?
Nah, it's fine.
Right, Hina?
Uh...
I'm Hina. Hina Adachi.
I'm 13 years old.
[NITTA'S MOM]
This looks great!
You sure do know your way around
the kitchen, don't you, bro?
From the looks of it,
I'd say you're enjoying your
new life at Yoshifumi's place.
Yeah, what's your
favorite thing about it?
Well, if I had to pick one,
the gentleman's club.
[coughs]
Huh?
[NITTA]
Uh. I mean.
She said she wanted to go.
All right, here's the thing.
On one hand,
it's no place for kids.
But then she looked at me
with those big puppy-dog eyes,
and I just couldn't tell her no!
Well, as long as you don't
take her there again.
[NITTA sighs]
That one was pretty easy.
I might be home free.
[NITTA'S MOM]
Let's have a few drinks.
[NITTA]
Yeah, why not?
Where'd the fireworks come from?
We had some visitors this
summer who brought their kids.
I guess they left 'em.
[MIKA]
Whatcha up to?
Hey.
We've got a killer over here!
Don't do that!
Their lives are
just as important
as anyone else's, Hina.
We're all friends in this world!
[HINA]
They're my friends?
You're right. I'm sorry.
What are you doing?
It's survival
of the fittest, kid.
Only the strong have
the power to decide
who lives and who dies.
My sister's insane.
Alcohol does that.
I wish you'd come over
and say hi more often.
I understand why you
keep your distance,
given the kind of work you do.
But we're still
your family, you know.
Yeah. I get it.
Raising Hina must
be a challenging job.
We'll try to help you
out however we can.
Thanks, it's pretty tough.
Not long ago, I got fed up
and kicked her out.
Then everybody was like, "but
you're the one who took her in.
You're a terrible dad!"
[NITTA'S MOM]
Did you just say, "dad"?
Uh...
[NITTA]
Oh, crap!
So much for being home free!
I'm confused.
Are you actually telling me
Hina's your daughter?
That's not what I said!
You'd better not be lying to
your own mother, Yoshifumi!
I'm not!
[HINA]
No, Nitta's telling the truth.
[NITTA'S MOM]
Sweetheart, uh...
I don't think you
understand what's going on.
[MIKA]
Leave Hina alone, Mom!
Poor kid's so traumatized, she
only remembers the chili shrimp!
Right?
Uh? The chili shrimp?
[HINA]
I've never had chili shrimp.
Is it chilly like ice cream?
[MIKA]
What are you talking about?
[NITTA]
She's trying her best!
Even though she doesn't actually
know what chili shrimp is.
Compared to her first few days
here, she's grown up so much!
She's dumb, but she's gotten
really obedient lately!
Still dumb, though.
What do you mean, "ice cream"?
Um. I was. You know.
[NITTA]
Don't worry about it, Hina.
Even if you are terrible
with context clues.
I'm still proud!
Hold up.
[NITTA]
I was lying earlier, Mom.
Hina's my daughter!
I knew it!
Bro! Why would you lie to us?
[NITTA] Well, I just
found out she existed,
and I didn't know what
the two of you would say
or if you'd believe me.
Either way, I've decided
to face this like a man!
You're kidding!
[NITTA'S MOM]
No, he isn't.
I see it in his eyes.
I'll want the details later.
But I am to understand
she's your real daughter, yes?
[NITTA]
Yep.
And I'm her dad.
[MIKA]
You don't sound old enough.
All right.
Then I'll say it like a grampa!
[laughs]
Dear.
[MIKA]
Yeah, I know.
First things first.
We need to drink a toast
to welcome the newest
member of the Nitta family!
Starting tonight, Hina,
you are one of us!
[NITTA FAMILY]
Cheers!
[HINA]
Owwie!
[NITTA'S MOM]
Look, darling.
Our Yoshifumi's
given us a granddaughter.
Y'know, I think you've got
your grandfather's eyes, Hina!
[NITTA laughs]
Yeah, I don't think so.
What's funny?
[NITTA]
Nothin' at all.
Don't you think you
should say a few words?
Hey there, pops.
Sorry you're not
still alive to meet her,
but Hina's your granddaughter.
[MIKA]
Is that all you got?
How's he s'posed to
hear you up in heaven?
Listen, pops, Hina's
one of the Nitta family now,
so I want you to watch over her!
[NITTA'S MOM]
Hey.
Yoshifumi.
Are you being the best father
you can be for little Hina?
[NITTA]
Hell, yeah!
Tell 'im, big bro.
I'm gonna take
care of that kid
and spoil her for the
rest of my life!
[NITTA FAMILY]
Yay! Yay! Ya!
Welcome to your
new family, Hina!
Your turn, kid!
Y' wanna get acquainted
with your old granddad?
[NITTA'S MOM, MIKA]
Go on!
Uh, well...
I...
I'm Hina Nitta.
I'm 13 years old.
[NITTA]
You can drop the act now.
[UTAKO] Let the homeless
keep their place!
[CROWD] Let the
homeless keep their place!
[UTAKO] They've got
nowhere else to stay!
[CROWD] They've
got nowhere else to stay!
[UTAKO] Let the homeless
keep their place!
[ANZU]
Hey, Yassan?
Huh?
What are all those people
yelling in the street for?
[YASSAN]
Uh...
I guess I better just tell you.
Huh?
I have a bit of bad news, Anzu.
It's about the park.
Sorry, but we have to leave.
Huh? Huuuh?!
[HOBO B]
I see.
So Anzu found out
about the park, huh?
It may not have lasted long,
but it sure was fun
havin' that kid around.
Remember how happy she was
when we built her little house?
And I'll never forget
making those cat's
cradles with her.
Me neither!
By the way, Yassan.
Did you straighten out
that deal with Utako?
[YASSAN] She said she found
someone to take care of Anzu.
This is the way it should be.
There's no place for us
in that little girl's future.
[GOTO]
As long as Anzu's happy.
[HOBO D]
Yeah.
[hammering]
All done!
Hey, guys!
Oh, Anzu.
We'd better start packing up.
Um.
What's that?
I thought we could hold up signs
like those people were doing.
[HOBOS]
Huh?
[sighs]
That'll draw too much attention.
There's nothin' we can do.
[ANZU]
We can't just give up!
What's the matter?
Hey! You'll help, right, Yassan?
We gotta stand up for our home!
Huh?
Sorry, Anzu.
[ANZU]
Fine.
I'll do it myself.
I won't let them take our park!
[YASSAN] If you make a fuss,
the police'll take you away!
We'll be all right.
[ANZU]
But, Yassan.
We're having a
farewell party later today.
Try to let it go and have fun.
A toast!
Unfortunately,
we're about to say goodbye
to a place we all love.
But here's wishing
for brighter days!
Cheers!
[ANZU]
Wait!
If we do end up losing the park,
then we can find
a new place together!
All of us, you'll see!
Don't hold your breath, kid.
We'll never find a spot
with enough room.
Sure we will!
We'll do it as a team,
like always!
That way, all of us--
[GOTO]
Give it a rest, would ya?
There won't be any
"all of us" after this!
We can barely take care of
our own selves these days!
Now be quiet!
[ANZU sobs]
[YASSAN]
Sorry you had to say that, Goto.
[GOTO] No, I said it
for selfish reasons.
I felt like she was tellin' me
I couldn't handle things on my
own, and I guess I lashed out.
What that girl doesn't know,
is how much
I regret living this way.
Dammit!
Hey, Anzu--
[GOTO]
Leave her be.
We said we'd skip the
tough goodbyes, remember?
[YASSAN]
Keep her safe, Utako.
Right.
[YASSAN]
Well, Anzu.
See you around.
Be good, now.
[SHIGE]
Grown men don't cry, Goto.
[GOTO]
Look who's talkin', Shige.
I see those tears!
[YASSAN]
Stop it!
[GOTO]
Yassan?
You too?
So you must be Anzu.
[UTAKO]
Mm-hm.
This is Mr. and Mrs. Hayashi,
the owners of Rairaiken.
You'll be living with
us for a while, okay?
[MRS. HAYASHI]
Oh, dear.
[MR. HAYASHI]
She's been through a lot.
[UTAKO] I gotta run.
Thanks again for your help.
[MR. HAYASHI]
Sure.
Go on, eat up.
[MR. HAYASHI]
Something wrong?
Aren't you hungry?
[ANZU] How much did you
pay for all this nice food?
Didn't cost us a thing!
It's nothing fancy,
but it's pretty good, isn't it?
[MR. HAYASHI]
You okay?
[MRS. HAYASHI]
Does it taste bad?
[ANZU]
Nuh-uh. It's great.
Everything's delicious, but...
[ANZU]
But...
I'm not sure if I deserve to eat
all this amazing food by myself.
I already feel
guilty for trying it!
What about the others?
They're out there on their own.
Why should I have it?
[MRS. HAYASHI]
Anzu.
You shouldn't think
about it that way.
[MR. HAYASHI]
Why don't you go get some rest?
[MRS. HAYASHI] Do you
think she'll like living here?
[MR. HAYASHI]
I'm sure she needs to adjust.
Let's just give
her a little time.
Poor thing.
She really is a good girl.
Kids like that make you want
to help 'em as much as you can.
New day.
Oh yeah, that's right.
I guess I don't have to go
digging for cans anymore.
But now I don't know
what to do with myself.
[ANZU]
Yassan.
Oh. Hey Anzu!
Good morning!
What are you doing?
[MRS. HAYASHI] We're about
to start work for the day.
You have work?
Let me help.
It's fine, no need
to trouble yourself.
[ANZU]
Nuh-uh.
If I'm not making any money,
then I'm not
earning the food I eat.
That's not how
we do things, dear.
Just a sec.
Did somebody tell
you that, Anzu?
Yeah, I learned it from Yassan.
Maybe we should try that, then.
Are you sure?
Yassan taught
her some good values,
and she's keeping them alive.
That's wonderful.
Huh? Keeping them alive?
[MR. HAYASHI]
Uh-huh.
You carry them
inside of your heart.
It's not just Yassan!
Everybody else
taught me stuff too!
Shige taught me how to get
cash for magazines I found.
And Hitomi showed me
where all those cans were!
They even helped me learn
how to build a house!
And there's more.
Lots more!
Exactly. Nobody can
live without other people.
Everyone you meet becomes
part of you in some way.
So my friends
are always with me?
That's right, and we'll
teach you things, too.
That way you'll have
even more people.
Yassan and the others carry you
in their hearts just the same,
I'll bet you anything.
Really?
But I never gave them
anything back.
[MR. HAYASHI]
Of course you did.
The memories of the time
you all spent together.
Those are priceless gifts!
Wow.
So...
[YASSAN]
Hello there, Shige.
Ah. Yassan.
You're worried
about Anzu, aren't you?
Oh, it's that obvious?
When we left
in a hurry like that,
I thought we were
doing right by her.
But after all the wrong turns
we've made in the past.
I'm wondering if that
was another mistake.
[SHIGE]
Well, think about it this way.
Huh?
We've got someone who's gonna
cry for us when we're gone,
so we'd better keep our
heads up a little longer.
[ANZU] Does that mean--they're
not alone either?
[MR. HAYASHI]
Never.
You're right there with them.
[ANZU sobs]
Good.
[MRS. HAYASHI]
Oh my, I need a tissue.
[MR. HAYASHI]
Get me one, too.
Now, now.
You can't get any work
done if you're crying.
[ANZU sobs]
'Kay.
[NITTA] Next time,
"Anzu Is a Greeter Now."