[HINA] I had lots of fun
living with you, Nitta.
Thanks for everything.
[HINA] I couldn't tell
you I was leaving.
I didn't really want to go,
and I was afraid of what
you might say about it.
But I have no choice.
I have to return home.
Because if I don't
do what they say,
they're gonna
rip my head off.
Are you ready
to get going, Hina?
[HINA]
Mm-hmm.
Bye forever, Nitta.
[IKARUGA]
Looks like I made it.
Despite Hina's presence here,
the city appears to be at peace.
[ANZU]
Back from deliveries!
[MRS. HAYASHI]
Welcome home!
Huh?
Well, if it isn't Anzu.
I assumed you had been killed.
You're the chief of... security.
Ika...
Ika-something.
Kei Ikaruga.
Why did you come here?
No, wait, I already know.
Don't do it in
front of them, okay?
Let's go somewhere quiet.
All right, go ahead
and finish me off.
Thanks, Mom and Pop.
You're the best!
I lived a pretty decent life!
[IKARUGA] Why are you
acting like you're going to die?
When you didn't come home,
you were classified K.I.A.
There'd be no point.
Huh?
I'm only here to investigate
Hina's behavior, Anzu.
You don't matter.
Feel free go on
living as you see fit.
[ANZU]
Did you just say I don't matter?
Hold on.
Is there any reason
to spy on Hina now?
You were sent out
to subdue Hina
after we discarded her
due to her lack of control,
but since she's too
powerful for us to properly
dispose of,
we've decided to learn
what we can from watching
her in her new surroundings.
[ANZU] Looks like stuff
a five-year-old could do.
[IKARUGA] The more
"yes" responses, the better.
[ANZU] Are you sure
this is a good idea?
Not much else we can do.
It is Hina.
[IKARUGA]
Nope, going home!
[ANZU] Wait! You haven't
done your job yet!
[IKARUGA]
I'm too young to die, Anzu!
Screw my stupid boss.
I'm only human!
I don't get paid
enough for this crap!
Can't be too hard.
You always got me
to listen to you.
[IKARUGA] But Hina destroyed
her collar when she snapped
and started wreaking
havoc on the city.
I have no way of
controlling her if she resists.
Makes sense.
By the way, how's she
been adjusting to this world?
A guy named Nitta started
taking care of her a while ago.
They're pretending
she's his daughter.
[gasps]
What a courageous man,
staring into the face
of death and destruction!
There she is.
[IKARUGA]
How did she get a broken leg?
I think she said Nitta
was spinning her around
and smacked her
into a wall really hard.
That man is a national hero!
I wonder what this
Nitta person's like?
He must work out.
Aren't you on a
mission or something?
There's no way any of
these are going to be a yes.
[gasps]
Wait a minute,
maybe I'll turn it in with
"no"s all the way down--
No, just do your job!
I'm familiar with Hina's habits,
so I know what to expect.
Red lights, for example.
[IKARUGA] If she's not given a
command, she'll probably destroy
the traffic signal and
wipe out the oncoming cars.
[IKARUGA]
She stopped?
I don't believe it.
That's impossible!
She's loaded!
Oh, hey there, Hina!
[HINA]
Hey.
[IKARUGA]
No.
This is the wrong girl!
[IKARUGA]
Low-ranking yakuza thugs.
Here we go.
She'll send those
three flying, for sure!
That's it, kill them!
--Kill them all!
--Whoa.
You're kidding.
It's starting to rain,
so we should probably
call it a day now.
[ANZU] You sure do
change your mind a lot.
Fine.
That was only the novice level.
I say we find out how she
scores on the advanced version.
[ANZU]
You just have to get a "no."
[IKARUGA]
I know exactly where to start.
[ANZU]
Huh?
I don't think there are
any animals around here.
[IKARUGA]
Hmph.
Then we'll get one from
that pet shop and leave it
in a box where she'll
see it on her way home.
[IKARUGA laughs]
I knew it all along,
that girl is a monster!
Look, she's even
stealing an umbrella!
She can't be stopped!
I bet that counts
for so many "no"s!
Hey, uh...
[IKARUGA]
No.
Nonononono!
Don't you do it!
[IKARUGA wails]
[IKARUGA]
"Cares for animals" is a yes!
[HINA]
You're homeless, huh?
I know what that's like.
So, what should we do now?
I guess I've lost.
Hina's really grown up
since she's been here,
much more than I anticipated.
[ANZU]
No.
I mean the puppy.
Woof.
Maybe you should take it.
I can't. I live in a restaurant.
[IKARUGA]
What?
I didn't see this!
"Addendum:
If this investigation
yields yeses
for over 90 percent of items.
Hina's psychological condition
will be deemed improved.
Therefore, she's
to be brought home."
What the heck?
They're running this
organization like loan sharks!
[MAMI]
I can't believe what I just saw!
She's telekinetic!
[MAMI]
This is incredible!
Hina's actually got powers!
And I'm probably the
first person to find out too!
Wait a second.
[VOICE B] "After witnessing
these bizarre phenomena,
Subject A reported
everything to the organization.
Subject A was
never heard from again."
[MAMI] I bet the organization
disposed of them!
[MAMI'S MOTHER]
Sweetheart, it's dinnertime!
Clean your plate, okay?
[MAMI]
Even if they try to silence me,
I, Mami Shinjou,
will never abandon
the mission set before me.
[MAMI]
Got a minute, Hitomi?
[HITOMI]
Sure, what's up?
[MAMI]
Well.
It's Hina.
Do you think she's hiding some
kind of unbelievable secret?
Secret?
I don't think so.
What is she to
you anyway, a friend?
Uh...
Nah, just another thing
that eats and sleeps.
[MAMI]
Wow, that's rough!
Does she know
how mean she sounds?
[TEACHER] Who knows what
Sentence A is describing?
[MAMI]
Man.
After all I've read
about telekinetic powers
and secret organizations,
I still have no idea how to
get information out of people!
What should I do?
Hey, she's talking to you.
Yes, Mommy?
Oh, my.
I'm not your mommy.
[MAMI]
Okay, that's it!
I'm just gonna have
to confront her directly!
Tell me, Hina.
You're a super-powered girl
created by the organization,
isn't that right?
How did you know?
[gasps]
[MAMI]
Oh, wow, so it is true!
Subscribing to Mar Monthly
was money well spent!
Can't let him find out.
[screams]
[MAMI]
Spare me!
I beg you!
I don't know.
[MAMI]
I'm sorry, okay?
I accidentally saw
you use your powers!
All I wanted to do was talk
to you about the organization
and bending spoons
and stuff, I swear!
Please don't make me disappear!
[MAMI] That's the coolest
thing I've ever heard, Hina!
So your powers just like
awakened out of the blue?
You can't tell anyone.
No problem!
I'm sure there's no such thing
as the organization, right?
[IKARUGA
"At least one friend."
"Yes."
You're so lucky!
No fair!
I know!
Can you teach me to
move stuff with my mind?
Huh? What for?
That'd make me awesome!
Just like you!
You're my hero!
Your hero?
That's weird.
Let me soak up
your coolness, Hina!
No, Master!
I'm calling you Master!
Teach me your ways!
Lend me strength!
So you're not kidding, then?
[MAMI]
Wow, that's crazy!
You make it look easy, Master!
Okay, here goes.
Up!
Nothing.
How does this even work?
Is there like a word?
Not really,
I kinda just feel it.
Oh. Feel it.
Right!
We're not leaving
till it works, are we?
[yellhs]
[gasps]
I... I did it!
I have the gift!
And I only trained for one day.
I must be some kind of genius.
That's great, let's go home.
Mami, dear?
Hey! Let's train
again after school!
Um. Yeah. Sure.
Yay!
I can't wait to learn more,
O Wise Master!
Check it out!
I'm totally on fire today!
Congrats, can we go now?
You know.
I've really gotten good
at this mind stuff.
I feel like I'm finally figuring
out how to connect the wires
in my brain to use my powers.
Mami.
Can we talk?
[HINA] Nobody can ever
know about your powers.
You can't use them
if I'm not around.
[MAMI] I know I have
to keep this a secret, but...
[MAMI] ...I want to brag
about it so bad!
[yells]
[MAMI] Who does she think
she is, telling me that?
I'm telekinetic,
just like she is!
She can't keep being
my master forever.
Hmph.
[KENGO]
Let's go, Takashi!
Yeah!
[MAMI]
Don't leave yet, guys!
I have something
I want to show you!
Gotta do it while she's asleep!
It might be hard
to believe this is real,
so look closely
and witness my power!
[chuckles]
There's a new
telekinetic in town, Hina!
Observe!
Now, I'll just reconnect
the wires in my brain, and...
Rise!
Rise! Come on, you
stupid thing, rise!
[HITOMI]
After that,
Mami Shinjou was never
seen or heard from again.
[MAMI'S MOTHER]
Mami, open the door, dear.
[HITOMI]
For two days.
[MAMI'S MOTHER]
Hello? Are you okay in there?
Answer me! Mami--
[HINA]
Yes, freedom is mine!
I'm Kei Ikaruga.
I'm from the organization.
And I've been sent here
to bring you back to them.
[HINA]
No.
[gasps]
You have no choice.
It's an order!
Order?
[HINA]
Fine.
[IKARUGA] Wow, that
was easier than I thought.
Well yeah, if I don't listen,
they'll pop off my head.
[IKARUGA] I get it, she still
thinks she has the collar on!
We leave in three days.
First, I have to find a
home for a stray puppy.
[HINA]
Mm-hmm.
[NITTA]
Augh!
[HINA barfs]
[NITTA]
You okay over there?
[HINA]
Nitta.
What's wrong?
[NITTA]
Uh...
[HINA]
Nitta.
Nitta!
Spit it out!
I'm gonna... I mean...
I have to...
[NITTA]
What is your problem?
[IKARUGA]
We leave in three days.
That's me, Nitta.
Where?
Are you trying to tell
me you're a foreign prince
disguising himself
as a little girl?
[NITTA] You're the ghost of
some ancient queen, then?
No, that's impossible.
[NITTA]
Says the super-powered freak!
Look.
Hina--
Time for breakfast, short stuff.
You there?
Okay.
Something's not right.
[HINA]
Owwie.
I'm sorry, we did
everything we could do, but...
...there was nothing wrong.
[NITTA]
Maybe a vacation?
Oh, do you think some good
seafood might cheer you up?
Wait. I... I don't think I'm--
[NITTA] That's it,
I've had enough of this!
Whatever you're hiding,
you better fess up!
Tell me right now!
Hey, calm down!
[HINA]
No trips, okay?
Are you evolving, or what?
[HINA] Sorry, but I've
been ordered to go home.
Huh? Come again?
[HINA]
And I have to leave today.
What?
[door opens]
[HINA]
Huh? That's it?
I was dreading it, too.
So much for my note.
[NITTA]
Let's go, Hina.
Huh?
Time's wasting.
Eat up, kid.
I'm gonna give you
one more good dinner.
They said
I could only eat stuff
that's easy to digest
after the gastroscope.
Who cares?
Do you want salmon roe
or porridge?
Salmon roe, hands down.
It's good.
It's just, my tummy
doesn't feel well.
[NITTA]
Is this spot okay?
[HINA]
Yeah.
Bye.
Look, Hina.
You were nothing but trouble
for me during your time here.
A grade-A pain in the ass.
But you're leaving,
and to be honest, the thought
of that is making my head spin.
Either way, having you
around--it was a lot of fun.
Yeah, I know.
[HINA]
Nitta?
I'm grateful for you.
[NITTA]
What was that?
Strange kid.
[NITTA]
Somewhere along the way.
I guess she grew up.
[IKARUGA]
Okay, time to go.
You brought your
orb with you, right?
[HINA]
Orb?
[IKARUGA]
The one you were encased in
when you first arrived here.
You gifteds need
those when you fly,
or else you could end up
at the wrong coordinates.
Umm...
That?
I lost it a long time ago.
[IKARUGA]
What? How?
Well, Nitta.
[NITTA]
What the hell?
This thing's a piece of garbage!
What is it even for?
He got mad and trashed it.
So, it's gone because a
grown man threw a tantrum?
[HINA]
That's what I said, isn't it?
[IKARUGA] Without that orb,
you have no way back home.
[HINA] That means
I can stay with Nitta!
[HINA]
I can't wait to see his face.
He must be so sad right now.
Maybe he's even crying!
Ni... tta.
[NITTA]
Uh, I can explain.
Start talking.
[HITOMI] Next time,
"Life Is About Survival."