[NITTA]
So, Hina.
Now that you're over
your food poisoning,
would you mind explaining to me
how you made such a huge mess?
You do know "cleaning"
means getting rid of messes,
right, ya little creepazoid?
Huh? Huh?
Ya got anything to say?
[groans]
And you broke my new vase.
I'm done with you!
Consider yourself disowned!
[NITTA] And don't even think
about breaking more stuff
to threaten me.
I'm not scared of you.
Bye, squirt.
Have a nice life, I guess.
Nitta. I'm sorr--
[NITTA]
Beat it.
I wonder what I should do now.
[HINA]
He gave me money for the road.
I should get some food.
Yay. Yay.
I'm out of money.
Now I'm really in trouble.
I guess I'll play a game.
[ANZU]
Hina?
Is that you?
[HINA]
Hm? Hey, Anzu.
I thought you went home already.
[ANZU]
Eh, long story.
It looks like I'm not the only
one who screwed up my life.
Tell him you're sorry!
[HINA] I tried that,
but he didn't forgive me.
Hey, this isn't enough food.
Got more?
[sighs]
You do have a
plan though, right?
[HINA] Yeah, getting
more food from you.
That was all!
[gasps]
I wish I could go back
to live with Nitta.
Well, I'll let you
stay with me for now.
Just figure things
out soon, okay?
You're loud.
Gah!
Owwie.
Right in the jugular.
Wake up, Hina.
It's morning.
[sighs]
I guess you don't have to.
Brought you
today's magazines, mister.
Oh. That's great, Anzu.
Thanks!
Here's your payment.
[ANZU]
Thank you!
[SHOP OWNER] You off
to collect some cans now?
Yeah.
See ya!
[ANZU]
Hina.
Hey.
Are you awake yet?
Who said you could eat that?
So?
Have you been thinking
of a plan at all?
[HINA] Yeah, but it is
a pretty complicated problem.
My game system's dead.
[groans]
No, not that!
[NITTA]
Ah.
Now that Hina's gone,
back to day-drinking.
[door bell]
What?
Dammit, Hina.
Go.
No more sob-stories.
Yes?
Uh. Hello!
I'm Mishima
from Watanabe Middle.
[NITTA]
Oh right, you're the bartender.
Nope, just Hina's classmate!
Anyway, I brought her
some handouts from school.
[NITTA]
Oh, thanks, that's nice.
Uh. Could you leave
'em in the mailbox?
Sure, but where's Hina?
Has she not been feeling well?
Uh, it's kind
of a personal issue.
She's with my family for now.
[HITOMI]
Oh, I see.
Yup. Take care, then.
Forgot about school.
[HITOMI]
That's odd.
I wonder why she
has to miss school?
I never know how to ask
about things like that.
[UTAKO]
Hitomi!
Thank goodness!
[HITOMI]
Miss Utako!
[UTAKO]
We need extra hands!
Come help us out!
[HITOMI]
With what?
Say, can you give me some extra?
Sorry, but there's a long line.
We have to be fair.
Okay, who's next?
[gasps]
Food, please.
[UTAKO]
What? Hina?
Oh, hey. It's you.
[UTAKO]
What are you doing here?
I'm hungry.
[ANZU]
Come on, I'm starving!
Oh. Sorry. Here.
[ANZU]
Okay, Hina, let's go.
[UTAKO]
Wait a second!
Hitomi, was it?
Thanks for your help.
[HITOMI]
Yeah, sure thing!
[UTAKO]
Hitomi!
Any idea what's been
going on with Hina?
Disowned her?
Uh-huh.
Why would you do that, Boss?
[NITTA] You don't know
how crazy it's been with her.
That brat costs me so
much money and headache,
and what do I get in return?
Nothing, zilch, nada!
Huh?
Raising kids isn't
about what you get back.
Yeah, and you're
the one who told her
she could move in with you.
[NITTA growls]
I know that, but still,
I'm not the kid's
father or anything!
Who cares?
You suck.
[groans]
[NITTA]
This'd be easier
if I could tell them
she fell out of the sky.
[BAR GOER A]
Jeez, man!
What's wrong with you?
Don't talk like that!
You're a bad parent!
[NITTA]
Aren't they just extras?
That was way too harsh, sir.
I can't even look
at you right now.
[NITTA]
Does he have a name, or...?
[ALL]
Go away! Go away! Go away!
[NITTA cries]
Hurry! Get the salt!
Right!
Hyaa!
Sabu!
Yeah?
[UTAKO] You'll have
to pay for Nitta's drink.
[SABU]
Aw, man.
[NITTA sighs]
I don't give a damn
if Hina's having a hard time
out there by herself!
Besides,
Anzu makes it work somehow.
She'll be all right, too.
I'm sitting in the one-seater,
just like when she was here.
I've picked up
some weird habits.
[ANZU]
Hina.
Candles cost money, you know.
[HINA]
Just a few more minutes.
[ANZU] And we could sell
that magazine to buy food.
But I'm bored
and almost out of chips.
Got more?
[ANZU]
That's it, I've had enough!
All you do is eat my food
and laze around all day!
You're not even trying
to come up with a plan!
Huh?
I can't deal with you!
Consider yourself disowned!
I wonder what I should do.
I sure miss living with Nitta.
How can I get him
to let me come back?
He got mad, because of the vase.
But still, I'm broke.
[gasps]
Ha! Another stellar performance!
Nice work, Atsushi.
As per usual.
[HINA]
Hey.
[ATSUSHI]
Huh? What's up, short stuff?
Did you see our concert?
Yeah.
What'd you think?
How'd ya like it?
[HINA]
I don't care.
I have a question.
Aww...
[NITTA sighs]
She was in line to get soup,
so she probably ended up going
to Anzu's place or something.
It's not like I'm worried
about Hina's safety,
but if she's dead,
I'm not gonna want something
like that on my conscience.
[ANZU]
Hey. It's you.
[NITTA]
Anzu!
[ANZU] Why are you
wandering around here?
[NITTA]
Um. Well, I... I'm out walking!
Really? Because
it sorta looks like
you're lurking outside of a park
like some kind of a weirdo.
Anyway, can we talk about Hina?
Huh? You gonna chew me out too?
[ANZU]
No.
It's just... I can't believe
you managed to put up with her
for as long as you did.
I kicked her out
after three days.
You what?
Hey, wait!
[ANZU] She's not even
fit to be homeless.
Aren't you insulting
yourself just as much there?
[CROWD ooos]
Nothing up my sleeve,
ladies and gents.
[MAN A]
That's amazing!
[MAN B]
How'd she do that?
[ATSUSHI]
Awesome, Hina!
I can't get enough of
those crazy magic tricks!
We've been the stars of this
neighborhood for a long time,
but you shine way brighter!
Why don't you come
to the afterparty?
Okay, why not?
[ATSUSHI]
Rock on!
[SABU] Hey, Boss,
I just caught sight of Hina.
[NITTA] I wish she'd come
home and apologize already.
She's really putting
a damper on my mood.
Whoa.
What the?
[ATSUSHI]
You guys have been so great!
I hate to call it a night,
but sadly, we've reached
the end of our show!
Remember, I'll always be your--
Let's say it together!
Angel!
[CROWD]
Hey, what gives?
This is too big a crowd.
And you don't have a permit.
All right show's over!
[ATSUSHI] See you again
tomorrow, everybody!
Wait, tomorrow?
[NITTA]
Am I drunk?
[ATSUSHI]
Man, we nailed it today!
I can just smell
that record deal!
You okay, Hina?
[HINA]
Sorry, you guys.
[HINA] I think I have
to leave the band.
You wanna walk out on us now?
We're gonna play
sold-out arenas, and--
Wait, Atsushi.
Check out the look on her face.
There's something you
need to do, isn't there?
[HINA]
Mm-hmm.
Man, what the hell.
Here's to you, Hina.
Whatever you're up to,
I'm sure it's punk rock!
[ALL]
Cheers!
[NITTA]
I told you, Utako,
the kid's doing
just fine on her own.
I was dumb to care.
I'm banning you
from the Little Song
until you make
amends with her.
Uh...
Who's he kidding?
He's obviously worried
sick about that girl.
[NITTA]
Hina.
Nitta.
Why are you here?
If I remember correctly,
I disowned you.
[HINA]
I'm sorry.
Why would you want to come back?
You've got a new life now.
[HINA] But I was happiest
whenever I was with you, Nitta.
[NITTA]
So what?
[HINA]
Hmm?
Just move so I can go inside.
[HINA]
No, wait!
For you.
Big deal. 'S a vase.
You were mad when
I broke your other one, so...
You brought me
this peace offering?
It's just a cheap knick-knack.
What did you pay?
Twenty-nine hundred.
I don't know how much money
the old one was worth, but here.
Nitta.
[NITTA]
Don't just stand there.
Get your stuff and come in.
Be back soon.
Hey!
I told you not to slam the door!
Damn kid.
[BABA] These days,
most places kick me out
when they hear I'm yakuza.
I'm tellin' ya, sweetheart,
it's a tough time to be
a yak around these parts.
Is that so?
[BABA]
Sorry 'bout that.
I shouldn't be
complaining so much
when it's my first time here.
Nitta told me right.
I'm the type of guy who lets
a good drink loosen my lips.
[HITOMI]
What's wrong with that?
Outside that door,
life is complex.
But whenever you're in here,
you can be completely
honest with yourself.
If you ask me, that's what
a good bar is supposed to be.
[BABA]
Hmph.
Hope to be back real soon.
Lately, I feel like I'm
gonna have to restructure
my entire teaching style.
The school board is
all over my back lately.
I know it's difficult,
but I'm sure there are students
who can see all the
hard work you put in.
Oh, Hitomi. Thank you.
I used to make drinks
for the satisfaction of seeing a
smile on a customer's face, too.
I guess I've lost that.
My thought process
is always: "I need money"
and "How can
I earn it in my sleep?"
[HITOMI]
There we go.
Working all-nighters
is really exhausting,
even if it's only
on the weekends!
Plus, my parents
are starting to suspect
I'm not staying
at a friend's house.
I should have a talk with Utako.
[HITOMI]
Hey, wait.
Isn't that the girl who collects
cans in the morning?
Um, can I help you?
Hi.
I'm Hitomi.
I work at the bar next door.
[ANZU]
Oh.
Well, I'm Anzu,
and I pick up cans.
I see.
Are you here doing
volunteer work, or...?
[ANZU]
Nah, I just sell 'em.
Yeah, it's kinda my job.
[HITOMI]
What kind of job is that?
Anyway. Bye.
Wait a second, please!
What? I'm trying to work here.
Could you come
with me somewhere?
Uh. Look.
I don't know you, and Yassan
says not to go with strangers.
[HITOMI]
Who's Yassan?
The one who's making
her dig garbage?
I'll take you to a place where
you can find a bunch of cans.
Huh?! Show me!
[HITOMI]
Mr. Abe?
[ABE]
Hey, Hitomi, what's up?
Your shop.
They throw out
lots of cans, correct?
[ABE]
Yeah, it's trash time right now.
They're over there.
[ANZU]
Whoa!
Would you mind
letting this girl
take them all off your hands?
[ABE]
Hmm? Oh yeah. You.
You scrounge for
cans around here a lot.
Don't ask me.
It's up to the boss.
[HITOMI] Your manager drinks
at my bar pretty often.
Huh?
You're always coming
out back to slack off.
Perhaps I should let him know?
Ah... Heh. You got me. Heh heh.
You drive a hard
bargain, Hitomi.
I'll let you pick up the
cans whenever I'm out here.
Just don't tell my boss
I'm goofin' off on the clock.
[ANZU]
Wow!
I got a whole bunch at once!
Thanks, Hitomi!
You're amazing!
Heh. It's not that
big of a deal.
[ANZU]
It's a huge deal!
Oh.
I know!
I should invite you over!
Yassan says it's important
to return people's favors.
[HITOMI]
Again, who is that?
But I want to go home and sleep.
Follow me, hurry!
[HITOMI]
This is awkward.
What must her family be like?
I assume they're extremely poor.
[ANZU]
Hey!
C'mon, over here!
[HITOMI]
The park?
Ta-dah!
[HITOMI] She lives in a shanty
in the middle of the park!
[screams]
[YASSAN]
Well, hello, who might this be?
[ANZU]
Yassan!
[HITOMI]
That's him?
[ANZU] This is Hitomi,
we met this morning.
Oh?
[HITOMI]
So, he's a homeless man.
A friend, eh?
Huh?
Uh, yes.
[HITOMI]
I guess.
Uh...
[ANZU]
I've never had a friend before.
So you're really my friend, huh?
Good for you.
[HITOMI]
I might regret this.
[ANZU]
I hope you're hungry!
I wanna treat you
to the fancy ramen!
They're two-hundred yen!
[HITOMI]
Uhh...
Um. Thanks a lot.
[ANZU] So how much money
do you make at your job?
Huh?
With all the work
I get done in a day.
I can make about 600 yen.
[HITOMI] I usually earn that
much in less than 30 minutes.
Ah. That's about
what I get paid.
Oh, really?
Well, it's not always the same.
One time I brought in 750!
That's my record.
Awesome, huh?
[HITOMI]
Sure is.
Uh-oh.
I don't think I can eat this.
Work's gonna be so much
easier from here on out!
No more walking around all day!
Well, that sounds
like an improvement!
This means you'll have more time
to hang out and have fun, right?
Sure will!
Hey, let's hang out now!
Huh? Oh, really?
[HITOMI]
Okay.
You're gonna be "it" all day!
[HITOMI] How long do
we have to keep playing tag?
Also, why are we playing tag?
Tag is stupid!
I'm so sleepy.
I can't go on.
Huh? Are you okay?
What's wrong?
[ANZU]
She fell asleep standing up!
[ANZU] Next time, "Three
Heads Are Better Than One."