Hyaaa!
[gasps]
She really is the world's top
practitioner of Naikaken.
Care to surrender?
[screams]
I knew I should've
purchased a life-proof case!
Luckily we all use the
"Find your Friends" App.
[MAO]
Hina. Just hang in there!
[NITTA]
It cost us two million?
No, you were right
to bid aggressively.
That vase is one of a kind.
Good work.
I should have a
respectable collection soon.
Long as profits keep up.
Thanks to the family,
I have more cash than
I know what to do with.
[laughs]
[grunts]
Ow!
[NITTA]
How many pills did I take today?
Huh? Hmm...
Ah?!
Cool.
Think I'll get an early night.
[NITTA]
Well, it's still here.
[HINA]
Hey.
[NITTA]
Hmm?
[HINA] Would you mind
undoing these restraints?
There's a button on the back.
[HINA]
Hey, can you hear me?
Yeah. All right, fine,
I'll do it.
What the--?
[gasps]
[HINA]
Clothing, please.
Huh?
Wait. You can't just barge
in here makin' demands.
How bout'cha get out of
my house, you crazy kid?
[NITTA]
Wait, no. No!
Those aren't insured yet.
[TV REPORTER A] Celebrity 1A,
who was recently released
on bond after being arrested for
possession of illegal drugs,
continues to deny--
Hey kid, feel free to help me
clean up the mess you made.
I have a name. Hina.
Ugh. Well tell me, Hina,
ya have any idea how much
these vases were wor--?
[sighs]
You're kidding me.
[NITTA] Listen up,
there are two trash bins.
That one's for combustibles!
Broken glass is not combustible!
Uh...
She could kill me
if she wanted to.
Wouldn't even be hard.
[gulps]
[NITTA]
Hina.
[HINA]
Hmm?
I'm curious.
Where'd you come from?
I can't tell you that.
Well, what's with that
weird power you used?
I can't tell you that.
Then, is there a reason
you showed up here?
Are you on some kind of mission?
Just hangin' out.
Seriously? Then why
don't you go back home?
I don't have one.
That sounds like a you problem.
No, no, no, not that one!
It's really expensive!
[shudders]
You know what?
You should stay for a while.
Ah!
My tongue has taken some damage.
[sighs]
Go lick some ice.
[NITTA]
You're dripping.
Use the blow dryer.
Blow dryer?
Fine.
Yet another male executive has--
[sighs] She should turn it
off when she goes to bed.
Huh?
This is weird.
Why do I feel like
I'm turning into a parent?
[HINA]
My lack of personal effects
has proven rather inconvenient.
Ooooo...
I'm sure it is,
but why do I have to be
the one to foot the bill?
[groans]
Fine, we'll get
whatever you want!
[HINA] I need one of
these to help me sleep.
[NITTA]
You slept just fine last night.
[HINA]
I need this.
[NITTA] Why's it gotta
be the expensive one?
[HINA]
It has a cute handle.
These clothes are cute.
I'm gonna need them all.
This place is amazing.
I feel like I could
shop here all day.
That'll be 857,120.
[NITTA groans]
[HINA's stomach growls]
I take it you're hungry.
[HINA]
Mm-hmm.
Fine, want something
in particular?
[HINA]
High-end sushi or Kobe beef.
[NITTA] You know Kobe
but not blow dryers.
Ohhh...
So this is high end sushi.
[sighs]
What the hell am I doing here?
[HINA]
There's no more salmon roe.
What should I do?
Ask for it.
[HINA]
More salmon roe.
[SERVER]
Sure!
You would be a
fan of salmon roe.
[HINA]
More salmon roe.
[SERVER]
Sure!
Heh. Look at you go.
More salmon roe.
Are you trying to
make me go bankrupt?
[TV REPORTER B] You may want to
start packing your kid's lunch.
Not only does school
cafeteria food look gross...
[sighs]
[NITTA] If you can
get her to stay put,
she's just your average brat.
[TV REPORTER B] In other news,
the Tokyo school board
has dismissed a
middle school vice principal.
A statement was issued charging
him with the misappropriation
and embezzlement of no less than
five million yen in PTA funds.
That sounds fun.
Huh?
I wanna go to middle school.
What about that sounded fun?
I'm sorry, but that's
not gonna work out.
Ya know what?
I'll make it happen, for you.
[sighs]
But we need to set
a few ground rules.
For what?
For how things need to go
if we're gonna live together.
Mm-hm. You have to stop
using those powers of yours.
If you're gonna go to school,
that's how it has to be.
We don't need you givin'
the lunch lady a heart attack.
Sound fair?
[HINA]
All right, you've got a deal.
Huh?
Pinky swear.
I saw it on TV.
Pinky promise, eye to eye.
If one should lie, then they
will cry, and bleed out and die.
[NITTA]
What did you watch?
[HINA]
Hmm...
So this is a teddy bear.
This Nitta is a grown-up.
Yet he gives me no orders.
I don't have to fight anyone.
What a strange place, this is.
[NITTA] Hey, you remembered to
brush your teeth, right?
Hmm?
[NITTA]
Huh...
So what was all that about
you needing a teddy bear
to help you sleep?
[MATSUTANI] Class, I'd like
to introduce someone.
Please join me in welcoming
your new classmate, Nitta.
Everybody, let's help
her feel at home.
Okay, Nitta.
Would you like to
say hello to the class?
Hey, Nitta.
Are you all right, Nitta?
Teacher. Nitta isn't here.
Did I mess up
another kid's name?
But it says it right here.
Hina Nitta.
You're gonna go by
Hina Nitta from now on.
At school,
they'll call ya Nitta.
But my name's Hina.
[NITTA]
Go with it, will ya?
Oh, my mistake.
Sorry, I forgot I'm Nitta.
[CLASS]
This girl has got some issues.
[MISHIMA] Yeah, but we were
in grade school ourselves
till last year.
So to put it bluntly,
the Shinozuka-gumi are pissed.
You might wanna lay
low for a while, boss.
Eh. Calm down, will ya?
Take a look at Nitta.
He's keeping his cool.
[NITTA]
I hope nothing goes wrong
with her first day at school.
[BABA]
Is he?
[NITTA]
It's fine.
If something goes wrong,
then I'll deal with it myself.
Whoa there.
Hmph. I like your spirit.
[MATSUTANI]
So, in conclusion, the namahage
is often mistaken for an oni,
due to their similar
appearances.
[MISHIMA]
She fell asleep?
--So, in conclusion...
--So, in conclusion....
So, in conclusion...
Aww yeah! Time for lunch!
[MISHIMA] I can't believe
she slept through
our first four classes.
Sorry to wake you,
Nitta, but it's lunchtime.
Hey, uh, Hina?
Don't freak,
but you're drooling.
Uh. Wait, don't use your sleeve.
Here. Let me.
[HITOMI] Weird. Why do I feel
like I'm turning into a parent?
[WORKOUT VO]
Keep your body relaxed
while you slowly bring your
hands around and then together.
Breathe slowly
as you hold this pose.
[HINA] I think I've earned
myself a sip of sport drink.
[NITTA] You have to stop using
those powers of yours.
I promised.
[NITTA]
I'm home.
And I brought a vase.
Listen, these
things are valuable,
so I can't have you
breaking them, okay?
Whoa, what's with the floating?
Stop floating!
What the heck happened in here?
I have to keep using my
powers, or I lose control.
[NITTA]
Why didn't you say that before?
My vases.
They're all gone.
You've taken everything
I love away from me.
[HINA] I was just trying
to keep my promise.
[NITTA] If you'd told me
that this would happen,
I wouldn't have
made you promise.
[HINA]
When are you making dinner?
[NITTA]
I'm gonna need a minute.
Will that blow-up
last you for a while?
That wasn't enough,
it'll happen again soon.
Huh? What am I supposed to do?
[NITTA] A hotel in
the Yamanashi mountains?
I'm not sure that's a
good idea right now, sir.
It's not my project. The
developers couldn't find anybody
who would clear the lot for
as cheap as they were hoping.
So they asked me
to see who I could find.
They don't care how it
gets done if it's cheap.
You sure these guys're legit?
If you can hook 'em up
with some discount contractors,
give 'em a call.
Ah, hell yeah!
[HINA]
Where are we going?
[NITTA] To a place where you can
use your powers all you want.
I'm hopin' this helps us avoid
a repeat of yesterday.
Aren't you gonna
scold me about it?
Why would I?
[HINA] I erred,
yet I'm not being punished.
I wonder where we're going.
It sounds exciting.
We're here.
The boss asked me to
handle this development job.
Think you can use your powers
to uproot them, like this?
I think so.
All right, then.
You can use your powers
all ya want here.
Understood.
[NITTA]
Yes!
This is awesome!
Can ya do more?
Yeah, sure.
Something like that?
[NITTA]
Fantastic!
[HINA]
Is that all?
Well, uh, actually,
if you don't mind,
could you make 'em like this?
[NITTA chortles]
Hell to the yes!
That was amazing.
It looks perfect!
[laughs]
Not a bad day's work.
We cleared the lot
and got lumber.
We made a killing today!
Damn.
If only there were a development
bubble goin' on right now.
I didn't realize how useful
your powers could be.
What's wrong?
I've seen that look before.
Huh?
Those grown-up eyes.
I know what it means
when people get that look.
I think I get it.
I'm sure lots of people
have taken advantage of you
because you're just a kid.
In that case--
[cell phone ringing]
[NITTA]
Yeah, what's up?
What? You've gotta be kidding!
All right. I'm on my way now.
[BABA]
Nitta! You think this is funny?
What about the boss
getting shot made ya think
this'd be a good day
to bring your brat? Huh?
I truly am sorry, chief.
Tried to take her home, but she
didn't wanna be alone there.
What, is she your boss?
[NITTA]
She twisted my arm.
So good. I've never
had tea of such quality.
It's from the hundred-yen store.
[BABA]
You're the boss's favorite.
And I remember you tellin' him
that if something went wrong,
you would deal with it yourself.
Well, here's your chance.
[NITTA]
Yes, sir.
[SABU] The guy we have
watching Shinozuka's house
hasn't seen him,
so I bet he's at his office.
All right, then.
[sighs]
The place'll be teeming
with his men.
I'm screwed.
Chief knows damn
well it's a suicide mission.
Guess this is how
yakuza get fired.
Damn it.
C'mon, Nitta.
There's gotta be
some way out of this.
[HINA]
Hey.
[screams]
Hina! Ya been back
there this whole time?
[HINA] Is someone in that
building an enemy?
[NITTA]
Huh?
Enemy?
[sighs]
Yeah, and I gotta beat him.
[HINA]
I'm ready for orders.
[NITTA]
Huh?
[NITTA] I didn't realize how
useful your powers could be.
You could order me to kill him,
so why don't you do it?
[sighs]
Have ya lost your mind, kid?
Huh?
Why should you have to
do something like that?
This isn't your
problem, all right?
[NITTA]
Hmm?
Hey, what're you...?
I'll do it anyway.
Where I come from,
my only reason for existing
was to carry out orders.
But you're not anything like the
grown-ups I knew in that place.
I like spending time
with you, Nitta.
Huh?! Hey, come back here!
[NITTA]
Whoa. She finally said my name.
Not the point, Nitta!
You can't let her
do your dirty work!
[NITTA]
Hina!
[HENCHMAN A]
Get outta here, kid.
Owie! Ow... ie...
[NITTA]
Uh...
[HENCHMAN B]
Die, you little bitch! Owie!
[HENCHMEN]
Owie! Owie! Owie!
[HENCHMAN E]
She went upstairs!
[HENCHMAN F]
What do you want? I'll kill you!
Owie!
[HENCHMEN]
Owie! Owie! Owie! Owie! Owie!
[SHINOZUKA]
Ow, ow, owie. Ow. Ow.
Is this one the boss?
Uh-huh.
[SHINOZUKA]
No fair.
Color me impressed, Nitta.
To think that you'd
single-handedly
defeat the Shinozuka-gumi!
Awesome.
He's a friggin' madman!
I'd follow him anywhere!
Huh?
I doubt that this'll come
as a surprise to you.
But in honor
of our victory here,
I've named you the
family's top soldier.
Well done!
[NITTA chuckles]
You really
shouldn't have, chief.
So good.
I've never had
tea of such quality.
Same cheap tea
you had last time.
[NITTA]
So Hina.
Is there anything I can get'cha?
[HINA]
Why?
You know, because
you helped me out.
But you bought me stuff earlier.
We made a boatload
of money today.
And when someone
does you a favor,
you should always get them back.
Well, how 'bout... salmon roe?
Hmph. Sounds good.
Whoa. What is this?
Best salmon roe bowl in town.
I had no idea that there was
a way to eat this much at once.
Why'd we bother with sushi?
[NITTA]
Say, Hina.
I don't know anything about
what your life was like
before I met you.
And I don't really want to know.
But out in the
world of grown-ups,
when you do good work,
you get a reward to match.
[HINA]
You mean I deserve this?
Thank you for this food.
All right, so how's it taste?
[HINA] I don't have
the words to describe it.
Good. Really, really, good.
That's all you
could come up with?
At last, I'm a
woman fully bloomed.
Absolutely not.
Nitta.
You are using organic
ingredients, right?
I refuse to be shamed for
cooking on a budget, okay?
What about our pinkie promise?
Well, I'm going to school now.
[NITTA]
'Kay.
Huh?
[NITTA]
Is this from...
...when Hina first showed up?
Hey, Nitta.
[HINA]
Ew.
Gross.
You looked just
as weird in this thing!
Hey. Wait. Come back!
You can't just leave me here!
Hina, come on, please!
I just have to hit that button.
One good roll into that
table and I'm a free man!
Oh yeah, here we go!
Not that way.
It's hopeless.
[NITTA]
Hina, please.
Press the button.
So I can make us breakfast.
[HINA]
Terminator.