[SHIGE]
There, all done.
[ANZU gasps]
[SHIGE]
If you practice,
you should be able
to do it yourself.
Wow! Thank you
so much, Shige!
[YASSAN] You act like you've
got a granddaughter, old man.
[SHIGE] I just did it
'cause I felt like it.
[ANZU]
Like this, and...
Ta-dah!
[gasps]
Oh no!
I lost track of the time!
I wasted a perfectly
good candle!
[sighs] Oh well.
[ANZU]
See, look!
Awesome, huh?
Just watch, I'll teach
you how to do it too!
But video games are more fun.
Fine, forget it, stupid.
You're nothing but
a big, dumb stupidhead!
[HINA]
Hmm...
Only stupid people
call people stupid.
[ANZU] Some of us
can't afford video games.
I'm so broke.
[ANZU]
Money.
Money. Money.
[ANZU sighs]
Money.
If I had some cash,
I could buy some games.
[ANZU]
What should I do?
I don't get it.
I used to be content
with the money I made
from walking
around town all day.
But now that I have time,
I want to do stuff.
Or maybe work more.
I dunno.
It's like I'm not satisfied
no matter what I'm doing.
I never knew human
happiness was so unattainable.
Feast your eyes on this, Hina!
What is it, though?
Yassan gave me a hot tip!
There's a homeless guy
named Yoshida
who buys electronics
people throw out!
Oh.
Look, he'll pay
3,000 yen for a TV!
[HINA]
Cool.
[ANZU]
C'mon, let's go look for one!
[HINA]
Where can we get TVs?
[ANZU]
I'm thinking somewhere deserted.
Hmm...
I know I've seen
a place like that.
People are so wasteful.
What about right there?
Holy crap, Hina!
We found the motherlode.
That was almost too easy!
It's like a giant
mountain of treasure!
You stand guard, Hina.
I'll be right back!
[HINA]
I'm tired.
[ANZU]
Hold on.
We're almost there!
[HINA]
Fine.
Your butt's making it heavier!
Yoshida!
[YOSHIDA]
Hmm? Hey, kid.
I guess word travels
fast around here.
[HINA]
You're pretty fancy for a hobo.
A hobo?
That's not nice.
[crash]
[ANZU shrieks]
No, my treasures!
[sobs]
You know those
are garbage, right?
You brought them for me?
I can't believe
you even bothered.
[ANZU]
But you wanted TVs!
Those old tube relics
are worthless nowadays.
I just buy 'em so I can
resell to Southeast Asia.
[ANZU]
So, how much?
[YOSHIDA]
Ten yen.
That's all?
[YOSHIDA] Three thousand
yen is only for HDTVs.
Those aren't nearly as
easy to come by as these.
But what does a hobo
want with a bunch of TVs?
[YOSHIDA]
You picking a fight with me?
[ANZU]
That's it.
[growls]
I'm all fired up.
I'll find you an HDTV,
no matter what!
Still no luck.
Wish we had more help.
I'm exhausted.
What? But I--
Hina?
I just called in
some reinforcements.
Huh?
Yeah, maybe I'd better ask
for help from my friend Hitomi.
Because she's
my friend and stuff.
Actually, I can't contact her,
even though she is my friend.
[HITOMI]
Hina?
Hitomi!
Oh. Anzu. Hey.
I'm confused.
The two of you know each other?
Yeah, we do.
Hina and I are classmates!
Oh. Right. I get it.
So, she was
your friend first, huh?
[sighs]
Hey, Anzu,
it's starting to get dark out.
Don't you think we
should call it a day soon?
[ANZU]
We can't.
We still haven't found
the right kind of TV,
even after you agreed
to help us look.
[HITOMI] Don't worry, Anzu,
we can look for a little longer.
I'll check for some over here.
[ANZU]
Great!
[HITOMI]
Hey, Mom, it's Hitomi.
Look, about that new TV
we just brought home.
I think I figured out
something useful we can do
with the old one.
Wow, Mom.
You didn't have to pack it up
in a box like I just bought it.
[HITOMI]
How about here?
Anzu's gonna be so happy!
[OFFICER]
Little girl!
[shrieks]
Uh...
What are you doing?
[HINA]
Hey. Can we be done now?
[ANZU]
We haven't found anything!
I wonder where Hitomi is.
She must be working hard.
[OFFICER] You can't leave large
items like that on the street.
You sure are quiet.
Nothing to say for yourself?
[HITOMI] If I told him
what I was up to,
he probably wouldn't believe me.
And if he did, that might
create even more of a problem!
[OFFICER]
Oh well.
Wait there while
I give your parents a call.
[HITOMI] Oh!
Please, sir, anything but that.
I'm sorry! No!
I'm too young to die.
[OFFICER]
Sorry to scare you, sweetie.
I've known the whole time.
It's okay, you can tell me.
Your mom and dad forced you
to dump that TV outside,
didn't they?
[HITOMI] I didn't expect
him to be that wrong.
[ANZU]
This is going nowhere!
Let's split off like Hitomi did,
so we can cover more ground!
[HINA]
There's a bunch.
[NITTA]
A TV?
[HINA]
Yeah.
But we already have
one in the living room.
[HINA]
It's not the same.
[NITTA]
Hmm...
That should be enough
to buy one, right?
Shouldn't you think
before you hand her
a wad of cash?
[NITTA]
Big deal.
I'm enjoying my drink.
I'd rather avoid
a family discussion.
[gasps]
Buy it from Bikkuri Camera!
For your perks card?
[CABBY]
Where to, miss?
[HINA]
The river.
[CABBY]
Seems legit.
[HINA]
Here you go, hobo.
[YOSHIDA]
Hold up.
This TV's factory-sealed.
Why would she sell this?
Maybe it's some kinda trick?
Huh, I can't get
a read on this twerp.
[CABBY]
Wait, miss!
You still have to pay
5,920 yen for the taxi fare!
But I'm out of money.
Huh?
Uh. That's all right.
I'll pay it.
As a handling fee for the TV.
Makes no difference to
me, I guess.
But you should know, she just
bought that at Bikkuri Camera.
What's she trying to pull?
[YOSHIDA]
Don't look at me, pal.
[ANZU]
Hina!
[sighs]
I still couldn't get any TVs.
Yeah, they're so hard to find.
I know.
Let's give up.
Huh? Huh?!
Am I seeing things?
It wasn't easy, but I succeeded.
I tried to plant it, but...
[ANZU]
You're the best!
What's wrong,
you don't seem very happy.
That's silly, of course I am.
Heh heh. See, I'm dying of joy.
[ANZU]
Wow, that's amazing,
you saved the day and
didn't let it go to your head!
[HITOMI]
Sure, that's it.
[YOSHIDA]
Another one in a box?
There's no way it's trash.
I know it goes against my best
interest to say this, but...
Just sell these at a pawn shop!
[ANZU] I didn't think we would
make anything at all today!
Are you sure you don't mind me
cashing in on the one you found?
Oh no, don't
worry about it, Anzu.
If you hadn't told
me you needed a TV,
I'm sure it would have just
ended up going to waste anyway.
The three of us should split it.
How's that sound?
Yeah, okay.
So, why did you try so hard
to get rich all of a sudden?
Uh...
Um, because...
Huh?
Well, I noticed you
liked video games,
so I wanted to
get one and play it with you.
I'm not telling!
[HITOMI]
You just did.
[HINA]
I'm home.
Hey. Did you pick out a TV?
[HINA]
Yeah.
Good for you.
I guess it'll be here
in a few days?
No, actually, I sold it.
You did what?
Where's the cash?
Not that that's
the main issue here.
I had to pay for a taxi.
Okay...? Start over.
[TAKASHI]
Kengo, wait!
[KENGO] We gotta get home,
or we're in big trouble!
Hey, that's Mishima!
Huh?
Yeah, you're right!
[KENGO]
Huh?
Isn't this a bar?
Why did she go in?
Huh? Look! It's Matsutani!
That was close!
Did he just go inside too?
Why would a teacher
meet a student at a bar?
[BOTH] Oh!
I bet they're doing dirty stuff!
[MATSUTANI]
Come closer!
[HITOMI]
So forbidden.
No!
[KENGO]
Wait, what happens next?
[TAKASHI]
Boob touch, duh!
[KENGO]
Then what?
I'm just a kid, Takashi.
I don't know how it works!
No fair!
I wanna grow up now!
Waaaah!
[KENGO] Does this mean
our teacher's a pedo?
[TAKASHI]
We should kick his butt!
Friends!
Thank you all for joining
us to address this crisis!
Uh, I'm the only one here.
Well, we couldn't
have word getting out.
Mishima's reputation
is at stake.
[SAYO] Hitomi wouldn't
do something like that!
Take it back, right now!
Yeah, listen, Inspector Aizawa.
The top brass never sees
what it's like on the ground.
[KENGO]
Mm-hmm.
If you want to play
detective, go bother Hina.
Uh, but she's so--
I know she's useless.
But if nothing else,
she can be the team mascot
or something, right?
[TAKASHI]
It's not a game!
All right, fine.
Sergeant Kengo,
get me Officer Hina.
Roger that, Captain Takashi!
[SAYO]
How old are you guys again?
[KENGO]
I brought in Officer Hina, sir!
So what's going on?
[TAKASHI]
Listen, rookie.
Just try not to get in the way.
Hey, you recruited her!
[TAKASHI]
Let's go over the plan.
Uh...
I'm going to
supervise this endeavor.
The Inspector?
I am Hitomi's friend, after all.
So unlike you clowns,
I won't stop
until I clear her name!
[TAKASHI]
That's our Inspector!
[KENGO]
You're so cool!
[HINA]
Um. I'm lost.
[SAYO]
I have my doubts.
But if there's even a chance.
So, Hitomi,
I saw you walk through
the entertainment
district last night.
[HITOMI gasps]
[SAYO]
Hmm?
[HITOMI]
No! I was.
Uh...
Oh! I... I was at prep school!
[SAYO]
At Kaishinjuku?
That's in the area.
[HITOMI]
Yeah, exactly.
[SAYO] There's a popular
teacher there named Yoshida.
Do you have him?
Um. Oh, no.
I'm not in Mr. Yoshida's class,
but I've heard good things!
[SAYO]
Oops, I meant Yoshino.
Golly gee! Him, yeah!
[SAYO]
Be right back.
[laughs] What kind of nerd
says "golly gee" and means it?
Ooh.
I wonder what other stupid
things I can get her to say.
No!
Sayo Aizawa never
forgets her mission!
[SAYO]
Sorry about that.
By the way,
those teachers don't exist.
[HITOMI]
Huh?
Of course!
Yeah, I knew
that the whole time.
I just didn't have the
heart to correct you, so...
Boy howdy, this is awkward.
I'm in quite a pickle here!
[SAYO]
I didn't think so at first,
but she is hiding something.
I guess she must be
in some kind of trouble.
Hey, Hitomi.
Have you been
to the Little Song?
[STUDENT] Gross,
Mishima's puking everywhere!
You got your
milk all over my face!
[TAKASHI]
Well she certainly overreacted.
So, have you, or not?
No way!
[SAYO]
Yeah, she has.
She's so cute
when she's terrified.
So, that Central Park band
you like has a new song.
Uh, Yeah, it's so good!
Oh wait, that was a lie too.
Stop it!
After intense interrogation,
the suspect never spilled.
Give it a rest, Aizawa.
you weren't even trying!
Yeah, all you did
was mess with her!
Well, Inspector?
[KENGO]
Say something, would ya?
Huh?
When she panics like that,
she's just too cute for words!
[KENGO]
Ugh, will you be serious?
Fine, we don't need you!
We'll crack the case on our own!
Oh yeah?
I'll believe that when I see it!
[TAKASHI] It's lame
if we leave the same way.
[SAYO]
There's only one staircase,
what do you want me to do?
I'm confused.
This sucks, Captain.
What now?
We keep looking for evidence.
If they're doing stuff,
we might catch 'em
alone together at school.
[gasps]
[KENGO]
At school?
You think they
would really, you know?
[TAKASHI]
Cut it out, Kengo.
Don't make me think about it!
Mishima.
Could you come with me
to the prep room please?
[HITOMI]
Sure.
[TAKASHI, KENGO gasp]
This guy doesn't waste time!
[HITOMI]
I'm coming in.
[KENGO]
The prep room.
[TAKASHI]
They're right behind that door.
What could they
be doing in there?
[HITOMI]
Oh no.
We shouldn't.
[TAKASHI] I still don't
know what comes next!
[KENGO]
Screw it, let's just bust in!
You're right!
Even if we happen
to see something,
it's for investigative purposes!
[KENGO]
True that!
[HITOMI screams]
[MATSUTANI]
What are you kids doing?
Ah, great, now the printouts
are all mixed up.
All right, boys.
Give Mishima a hand here.
Uh. Hey, Mishima?
[HITOMI]
Yes, Takashi?
Are you doing anything
weird you can't tell us about?
[HITOMI]
Huh?
That came out of nowhere.
[TAKASHI, KENGO]
She's got "guilty" written
all over her face!
[KENGO]
You dummy!
What you're doing is wrong!
You think it's bad?
I mean, I have
to keep it secret,
but it's really gratifying!
Gratifying?
Uh, well, it would
be if there was something!
Kengo!
[HITOMI]
The printouts...?
[TAKASHI]
Matsutani!
Mark my words.
We'll catch you one day!
And we'll finally know
what happens next!
All that aside,
did they really have to
throw these on the floor?
Well? Is the case closed?
[KENGO] We want you back
on the squad, Aizawa.
[TAKASHI]
I just know the answer's
right around the next corner.
[KENGO]
And once we find it,
we'll make sure that teacher
pays for his despicable crimes.
[SAYO] Do you
hear yourselves right now?
[KENGO]
Huh? Look, there she is!
She went in!
It is true!
[TAKASHI]
And now, we wait.
Wait for what?
[KENGO]
Where's Matsutani?
[HINA]
Still confused.
[TAKASHI]
Maybe we had it wrong.
[KENGO]
Hmm. Y'think so?
Yeah. What if she
does it with lots of guys.
You know, for money
or something?
Hitomi would never do that!
You can't ignore facts.
She even told us
it was gratifying!
Oh. Nitta.
By "Nitta," you mean your dad?
[HINA]
Mm-hmm.
Huh? He's not.
Is he?
[TAKASHI, KENGO] He's
totally here to see Mishima!
Oh crap. No way!
Does this mean Mishima's
on a date with Hina's dad?
Gross!
How 'bout that?
I hope you're happy
with your future mommy!
Calm down, man,
this is a crime scene!
They're at a bar!
So, plenty of love
stories begin in a bar!
Don't be such an idiot!
If their love begins here, then
I'll make sure it ends here too!
[SAYO] C'mon, Hitomi,
please don't be doing
what I think you're doing.
Please!
[HITOMI]
Welco--
[gasps]
[BOTH gasp]
Uh....
[silent screaming]
Inspector?
Should we be
freaked out or relieved?
I have no clue.
Well, whatever's happening,
it isn't what we thought.
Huh. Yeah. I guess not!
It could be a lot worse!
Not cool, Mishima.
You had us worried!
Why are you bartending?
[HITOMI]
Boys and girls.
Sorry, but children
aren't allowed in bars.
Whoa. She's really
going to play dumb!
Do you seriously think you
can fool us with that trick?
Yeah! What's your deal?
The target's getting
belligerent, Inspector!
This takes finesse!
Fess up or else!
[TAKASHI]
Tell us your address, miss.
Uh. Please don't make
a scene at my workplace.
She gonna survive this?
Doesn't look that way, does it?
[SAYO]
Hitomi.
Truth is, we did all this stuff
because we were
concerned for you.
It's fine if you
keep it to yourself.
The only thing I need to know,
is whether or not you're okay.
You scared me.
'Cause I care about you.
We're friends, right?
I'm sorry, Sayo.
I promise I'm all right.
[SAYO]
Oh? Is that so?
Huh?
How did you know my first name
was Sayo, Miss Bartender?
[shrieks]
The gig is up, Mishima.
Your mother's gonna
be so disappointed in you.
Sorry. I should've
told you guys.
[SAYO] I want to hear
an official confession.
Say, "I'm a middle
school student
who secretly
works as a bartender."
I'm a middle school student
who secretly
works as a bartender.
Again!
Uh, I'm a middle school student
who secretly works
as a bartender!
Come on, louder!
Fine. I'm a middle
school student
who secretly works
as a bartender!
[SAYO]
I can't hear you!
[HITOMI]
I'm a middle school student
who secretly works
as a bartender!
[SAYO]
Once more with feeling,
like a pop star
playing a concert!
[HITOMI]
I'm a middle school student
who secretly works as
a bartender. Now, let's rock!
What is this?
I still don't know.
Someone tell me.
[MATSUTANI]
Huh?
You again?
What are you three
doing in a bar?
[KENGO]
Uh-oh!
Matsutani!
[MATSUTANI]
Oh, I get it!
You mistook her
for Mishima, didn't you?
Nope, Hitomi just
looks exactly like her!
[ALL 3] How does someone that
stupid get to become a teacher?
[HINA] Next time;
"Nitta- san Has a Dandy Dad."