[birds chirping]
[barking]
[chuckling]
[gasps]
[HIROTO] There he is, my
people-hating childhood friend.
Subaru Mikazuki.
[gasps]
Guess he’s getting used
to having a cat in the house.
He’s never had one before.
[chuckles]
[grunts]
[hissing]
[SUBARU sighs]
I’ll never get used to this.
What the hell?
Why do cats go all spastic
for no reason like that?
[SUBARU grunts]
[groaning]
[SUBARU]
You little...
Using my stomach
as a springboard?
-[clattering]
--[SUBARU gasps]
What did it do now?
[groans]
[SUBARU groans]
[growls]
Damn you, cat!
[SUBARU]
Stupid cat.
Why did you have to jump
on my parents’ altar?
What is your freaking problem?
I hope you’re sorry, at least.
[sighs]
You couldn’t care less,
could you?
-Of course not.
-[cell phone rings]
Hello?
Why do you always make me
leave my house to meet with you
when everything you say could be
covered in a phone call?
Well, you know,
seeing you in person
beats talking on the phone.
I really prefer
face-to-face conversation.
That makes it easier
to communicate the details.
Hey! We should check
out that robot café!
-Everyone’s talking about it!
-[SUBARU gasps]
[KAWASE] I hear they even have
a robot working the register!
[meowing]
[KAWASE] Huh? What’s that sound?
Do you have cats with you?
[SUBARU]
Yeah, I do, in fact.
They’ve been frequenting
my yard lately.
[KAWASE] Oh. Well, in that case,
I’ll be right over!
[cell phone beeps]
[SUBARU] Who cares about
stupid robots?
I’d prefer to have
a robot for an editor.
What the hell is wrong
with people?
♪
Ever since that day,
being alone makes me feel
their absence even more.
But being around other people?
That’s almost unbearable.
[STUDENT 1] Hey, check out
Mikazuki over there.
Reading a book, as usual!
[STUDENT 2]
Wait, for real?
[STUDENT 3]
That guy is the lamest ever.
[STUDENT 4]
Shut up, dude! He’ll hear you!
[STUDENT 3]
Meh. Who cares?
Oh, did you guys think
about my idea?
[SUBARU]
Reading is way more fun
than the dumb things
you guys like to do.
Such pains in the ass.
[SUBARU] Summer break is my
favorite time of the year!
I can read all day, every day,
without anybody bugging me!
Subaru! Guess what?
Your dad just found out
he gets an extra week
of vacation time off!
I was thinking the three of us
could take a trip!
Mom, haven’t
I asked you to knock?
I mean, how many times
do I have to tell you
I don’t like going on trips.
Where should we go?
I told you, I’m not going!
[chuckles] Yeah, yeah.
[SUBARU]
How could a kid like me
have been born
to parents like them?
People who took trips
every chance they got.
I guess it’s too late to wonder.
Now I’ll never know.
[doorbell rings]
You said there were cats,
so I rushed over!
Well, where are
all the kitties, then?
-[SUBARU] I already ran ‘em off.
-[KAWASE groans]
-[KAWASE sobbing]
-Uh, Kawase...
Is that the only reason
you’re here?
We might as well
have our meeting,
unless you’re
just here for cats.
[KAWASE]
Oh! Actually,
I know a great place
nearby we could go.
How many times
do I have to tell you
that I do not like going out?
[KAWASE] If you stay
in your house all the time,
you’re gonna end up
getting fat.
Right. Fat and happy.
[KAWASE gasps]
♪
Gah! Hold on, Mikazuki.
Could that be what I think?
The cat?
Yeah, I took it in a while ago.
Don’t tell me, you’ve become
a cat person now, haven’t you?
-Wha-- ? No, I--
-What’s this angel’s name?
Uh, it’s Haru.
[gasping]
May-- May I have the honor
of petting her?
[SUBARU]
Her?
-Yeah, whatever.
-Hello, Haru!
I’m gonna pet you
just a little, okay?
How does that sound to you?
Just a couple scritches.
Hey, Haru! Here, kitty!
Kitty-kitty-kitty.
[laughs] Bet you were a stray.
That’s why you’re so nimble!
[SUBARU] What on Earth
is so great about this?
I’ve got it!
What do you think
about this idea:
From now on,
we can have our meetings here!
Hold on, you want to meet
at my house every time?
Our friendship is still new.
This is a great way
to deepen it!
[SUBARU] What the hell
is he talking about?
Besides, Mikazuki,
it’ll be more pleasant for you,
since you don’t like
to leave the house.
Isn’t that right,
Miss Meowsers!
Well, he does have
a point there.
If I don’t have to go out
and deal with crowds
of noisy people,
it doesn’t get
much better than that.
♪
Anyway, our meetings
are sporadic.
They don’t happen
but a few times...
-every... month.
-[KAWASE] Me, again!
[laughing]
[SUBARU] Man! They were never
this frequent before!
Why the hell’s
he here every day?
Um, Kawase?
This is kind of
an awkward question,
but are you here to work
or play with the cat?
Huh? Oh, don’t worry!
I brought my work!
I don’t have to go in today.
That’s what you have
an office for!
I’m so sorry.
I just really
adore cats, is all.
But I can’t have one
because my wife is allergic.
When I saw you had one,
I guess I got a little carried
away trying to play with it.
[SUBARU]
To be perfectly frank,
Haru’s just not interested
in playing with you.
Well, you sure
don’t mince words, do you?
Hey, uh...
This might sound kind of weird,
but would you mind
holding her for a bit?
That might make her a little
less nervous around me.
I don’t know. I mean...
I’ve hardly even
touched the thing.
Wait, you don’t,
like, pet her?
-I don’t.
-Or floof her fur?
Floof? What’s that?
Oh. I did touch her
when I brought her home.
Are you serious?
You have such an adorable
little kitty-cat,
-but you--
-[HARU hisses]
[KAWASE grunts]
[SUBARU] Kawase!
Are you badly hurt?
I’m fine. I must’ve spooked her
a little, that’s all.
I guess I got what I deserved.
Oh! Would you
look at the time?
Well, Mikazuki,
I gotta head out now.
All right.
Have a nice workday.
I’ll see you in the morning.
[SUBARU]
He’s coming back tomorrow?
[KAWASE chuckles]
[sighs]
I just want
my quiet life back.
[HARU meowing]
[SUBARU sighs]
[SUBARU] You know why he’s
so persistent, right?
It’s ‘cause you’re ignoring him.
I mean...
You could be
a little friendlier.
[TEACHER]
All right, boys.
We need to be friendly
when we’re playing, okay?
[SUBARU]
I just want to read my book.
Never mind. You do your thing.
♪
[SUBARU] Ugh.
I’m getting so tired
of these endless interruptions
for no good reason at all!
[SUBARU gasps]
Hey!
Is everyone insane?
Why can’t anyone try to consider
how I might feel?
[rain pouring]
Out of ink already?
Ah, well, dammit.
Out of spare cartridges, too.
Feels like forever
since the last time
I went into Mom
and Dad’s room.
Hi, there. Subaru?
[breathes shakily]
What is it, dear?
Haru, you stay out of here.
I don’t want you playing in--
[hissing]
[SUBARU]
You are a pain in my ass.
[coughing]
Dang, these things are dusty.
Oh. One of Mom’s old albums.
This brings back memories.
She always enjoyed
putting these things together.
What’s that?
One of her notes.
“Not good to visit
during the day,
"because of all the tourists.
It’d be better to come later
in the evening.”
What is all this?
[SUBARU'S MOM] Hey, you can
still come with us if you want.
-It’s not too late.
-What are you talking about?
Come on.
Go, or you’ll miss your bus.
[SUBARU'S MOM]
Okay.
[SUBARU'S DAD] Look after
things here while we’re gone.
You sure you won’t come?
[SUBARU] If only I had
stopped them from going.
“Traveling just
makes me tired.”
I made that excuse every time,
and turned them down.
But they never
stopped inviting me.
To be honest,
I’d gotten sick of it.
[SUBARU'S MOM]
You sure you won’t come?
[SUBARU]
How must they have felt...
Next time, we can take a trip
somewhere you want to go.
[SUBARU] ...as they stood there,
smiling at me like that?
I never cared enough
to find out.
And I lost my chance.
[SUBARU crying]
It’s too late.
They’re both gone.
[SUBARU sobbing]
What do you want?
Don’t you have food
in your bowl?
Please go away.
I want to be alone.
[SUBARU gasps]
What the--?
Why did you just--
Why doesn’t anyone ever take
my feelings into consideration?
But, I didn’t do that
for them, either.
I wonder if there’s still time.
Even for someone like me.
-[energy humming]
-[SUBARU gasps]
She’s so warm.
I didn’t expect that.
[chuckles]
[HARU]
He’s touching me.
I never expected
this human to do that.
♪
[HARU]
Yes! This house is great.
It has so many nice places
to take a nap!
And I have delicious food, too.
I really like it here.
Or so I thought!
What are those?
They’re so scary!
There shouldn’t be
anything living in this house
except for me and that human!
[shrieks]
When they get close,
everything feels cold!
And I can’t catch them, either!
[HARU grunting]
Did... Did I scare them away?
[HARU]
Huh?
I have to get rid of them!
Or they’re gonna steal
all my favorite spots!
Looks like I can’t expect
any help from that human.
It’s up to me.
I’ll get ‘em!
[SUBARU groans]
[HARU] You met your match,
creepy things!
You won’t get away this time!
Get out of this house,
and never come back!
[clattering]
[hisses]
Huh? Did I really
scare them away?
[SUBARU growls]
-[SUBARU] Damn you, cat!
-[HARU shrieks]
[HARU whimpers]
[HARU] What’s wrong?
He was so loud.
I’ve never seen the human
like that before.
Anyway,
I just need to calm down.
That guy from earlier.
I hope he’s gone by now.
-[footsteps approaching]
-[HARU] Hmm?
He hasn’t used
that loud voice again.
I wonder what that was about.
Huh?
Haru, you stay out of here.
[HARU gasps]
[HARU]
They’re back!
Those things
just refuse to give up!
Get out of here!
[screams]
This house belongs
to me and him!
I will not let you have it!
[hissing]
-[HARU] Huh?
-[SUBARU sobbing]
[HARU] Wait.
What’s going on?
[HARU growls]
[cawing]
[yells] Get away from him,
you nasty pink things!
[whooshing]
I guess you were scared
of those guys, too, huh?
But it’s okay. Look!
They’re gone now.
Honestly, you’re completely
helpless, human.
You’re a grown man, aren’t you?
Come on, it’s all right!
I’m here to protect you
from stuff!
I’ll always be. No matter what.
I'll be right here.
Oh, that startled me.
But, I guess...
This might not be so bad.
[sighs happily]
[rain pouring]
[HARU startles]
Huh?
[HARU gasps]
[hissing]
You guys are back again?
Thank you so much.
Huh.
[HARU]
That was kinda weird.
-[doorbell rings]
-[HARU meows]
[KAWASE] Mikazuki!
Are you okay? Open up!
[panting]
[KAWASE] Oh, thank goodness!
I couldn’t get a hold of you.
I thought maybe
you’d passed out again. Phew.
I’m sorry. I just drifted off.
[KAWASE]
Your eyes are red.
Did you get
any sleep last night?
Uh, that’s because...
[gasps]
[SUBARU]
He ran over in the rain.
Got himself soaked.
Listen. Kawase.
-I want to thank--
-Hi, Haru!
[HARU screams]
[KAWASE]
You came to say hello?
Such a sweet kitty!
And so cute!
Kawase, would you like
to feed her?
What? For real?
[SUBARU]
Uh, yeah.
[sighs] Precious kitty!
[laughs]
-[sighs contentedly]
-[eager munching]
[laughs softly]
[HARU]
I just love the smell of food!
[TARO]
I just love the smell of humans!
[HARU]
I think naps are the best!
[TARO]
I think walks are better!
We’re lucky to have
so many things to love.