[HARU]
What's going on with the human?
[grunting]
He's acting kind of strange.
Something's definitely up.
Most days,
he's usually like this.
But today he's like this.
[muttering]
[frustrated groan]
[HARU]
Hey, human, are you okay?
Did you make sure
and eat all your food?
Where are you going?
I don't want you
falling over again!
Wait!
Don't worry, I left some
extra food in your bowl.
I don't have any time
to hang out, though.
[HARU]
How dare you?
Well, I refuse to worry
about you anymore, got it?
Fine, then!
At least now I can nap
without anyone bothering me!
[sighs]
This is pretty much paradise.
[TARO]
Kitty!
[HARU]
Huh? What was that?
[TARO]
Hi, wanna play?
[HARU]
For real?
All I wanna do is nap.
[TARO]
Come on, let's play together!
None of my humans
are around here today.
So, I'm stuck
being all by myself.
I feel lonely.
I hope they come home real soon.
[HARU]
I'm all alone, too.
But what is that word he used?
"Lonely"? What's that mean?
[TARO] Huh? It's the man
from the meat place!
Hey, there, Taro, my buddy!
[TARO]
Aw, yeah! Pets!
[MAN] Who's a good boy?
You are! Yes, you are!
[HARU] Ugh, finally.
Some peace and quiet.
Hey, that's my food,
put that down right now!
Huh?
Hold on. What?
Where did all the food go?
I swear it was just here.
[yawns]
Oh, that's right!
Mm, so tasty!
Wait, gone already?
But I'm not even full yet.
Hey, give me more food!
Need some food in here!
Hang on, where is he?
Has he seriously
not come back yet?
Oh! I've got it!
[whimpers]
But, he's always in here.
Human?
[whimpers]
The smell in here is relaxing,
and this place is cozy.
But, still...
[TARO] So, I'm stuck
being all by myself.
I feel lonely.
[HARU] "Lonely."
Is that what this feeling is?
Nuh-uh!
Being here alone is no big deal!
I mean, I'm super strong!
I can totally live on my own!
It's not about that.
I'm just worried
about that human!
That's all! Humph!
Anyway, it's nice
and warm in here.
Although, if the human
were here with me,
it would feel even warmer.
[gate creaks]
[gasps] I know that sound!
It means he's home! Huh?
[TARO laughing]
[TARO]
Welcome home! I love you!
You're glad to see us,
and you've been
such a good boy
guarding the house today!
[HARU sighs]
Where is he?
He's never gone this long.
So, why? Why isn't he here?
I don't like it!
[screams]
What the heck is happening?
-[crashing]
-[angry grunts]
You better come home
right now, human!
-[angry grunting, screaming]
-[clawing]
[TARO] Oh, my goodness,
little kitty. What's wrong?
You need to calm down!
-Where the heck is that human?
-[gnawing]
[SUBARU] Why the heck
did I agree to this?
[KAWASE]
Thanks for your patience, folks.
Sorry to keep you all waiting.
Without further ado,
welcome to the first
official signing
for Subaru Mikazuki's
"Shining in the Dark of Night!"
Wow. We announced
this on short notice.
And despite that,
so many of you showed up!
I'm thrilled to see
such a large crowd!
You don't know how
happy that makes us.
Isn't that right, Mikazuki?
-Oh, no.
-[SUBARU] Take me home.
I can't do this!
Hey, Mikazuki!
You sure you're
feeling all right?
I wasn't in my right mind
when I agreed!
I didn't think the whole
thing through at all.
My instincts were right.
I can't handle this kind
of human interaction. Save me!
[KAWASE] It's okay.
Just take a deep breath.
Come on. Sit down.
Here.
Oh, your tie is
a little crooked.
[SUBARU]
Take me home.
[KAWASE]
It's okay. I'm right here.
[SUBARU]
Nothing is okay right now!
[KAWASE] All right, first guest,
we're ready for you!
-This is so exciting!
-Uh. Hi. Hello.
I've got this.
Just have to write my name.
Don't think about
anything else.
Be careful,
and make sure it's straight.
If I can just manage that...
It's crooked!
And in permanent marker!
I can't rewrite it!
Um, I'm so sorry.
It's crooked.
It's hopeless. I can tell
he's disappointed. I knew it.
I was an idiot for thinking
I could handle
something like this.
Oh, man! I'm gonna treasure it!
Keep up the great work!
-Huh?
-Thank you so much for coming!
Wow.
Thanks for being here today.
[SUBARU] They don't care
if my writing is sloppy.
Whoa, awesome! I'm your
biggest fan! Thanks so much!
[SUBARU] They're just happy
to be meeting me.
[FAN] From the very first page,
I could not put it down!
I was dying to find out
what was going to happen next!
I stayed up all night
and finished the whole thing
in one sitting!
-I'm exactly like you!
-Huh?
Wait, no, what I meant
to say is that I...
Yep, I think a lot of us
book worms can relate!
Oh, I understand. You've gotten
swept up by a novel, too?
And you stayed up
all night reading?
[SUBARU] How frustrating.
The words won't come out.
I write for a living.
Why can't I speak?
Um, sorry.
Wait, I mean... I, uh...
Well, hello!
There's no need
to be nervous, sir!
Uh, right. I guess not.
I... I just love this book!
And I've read it over
and over again!
I think it's my favorite ever!
Um, I'd be honored
to shake your hand!
[SUBARU]
Have I ever had the courage
to reach out
to anyone like this?
Let alone someone I admired?
Nope, I'm a chicken.
Once he starts talking
about that cat story,
you can't get him to stop!
Come on. I'm telling you, bro.
The cat's awesome.
[SUBARU] I couldn't even tell
them I'm the one who wrote it.
I don't deserve
to be here right now.
No. I'm honored.
That means the world to me.
Um, my name is Kota Iijima.
If you don't mind,
can you address
the inscription to me?
Ha!
[KAWASE] Whelp,
just about time to wrap up.
Thanks so much for all
your hard work today.
Uh, Mikazuki?
Is something the matter?
[SUBARU] Oh. No,
although... Just occurred to me,
I didn't thank anyone
in the first part of the day.
After all, they came to see me.
[KAWASE]
Let yourself off the hook.
Nobody does everything
perfectly, you know.
Just do your best
to thank everyone next time.
And until then,
we'll be working hard.
So there'll be a next time.
I really appreciate that.
Uh, I'll walk through the store.
There might be some stragglers,
and we don't want to leave
any book unsigned!
[SUBARU] Just beyond my fear
of reaching out,
there is more warmth than
I could have expected.
When I stop to think about it,
there's warmth
everywhere I look.
That reminds me.
She was meowing more
than usual before I left.
I was in a hurry, so I didn't
have time to find out why.
I left her food and water,
and her litter box
should be fine.
Is this the first time
I've been away from home
this long since I got her?
I hope she's okay.
[KAWASE] Right this way, Miss.
Ah, Mikazuki, look!
I found one last reader.
She rushed here to catch you.
[SUBARU]
Wha-- ? Oh. Uh, hello.
[NANA] Sorry I'm late!
I'm so glad I made it in time!
My younger brother
is also a big fan of yours,
but he couldn't make it.
He was so disappointed!
I thought I'd pop over here
in his place
and surprise him
by getting your autograph!
[BOTH]
Huh?
-[SUBARU] Huh?
-[NANA] Wait, Subaru?
-What are you-- ? Huh?
-[SUBARU] Okami?
[BOTH]
Huh?
[NANA]
Does this mean you're Mikazuki?
The Subaru Mikazuki?
[SUBARU]
I can't believe it.
I never imagined
this would happen!
Wait. Oh, gosh. Did I-- ?
I did. I totally talked to you
about "Shining in
the Dark of Night!"
Yeah. I couldn't bring myself
to tell you who I was that day.
Why? I sat there like a jerk,
not saying anything.
How is that any different
than lying to them?
She must think
I'm a complete ass.
No, it's even worse than that.
She probably feels betrayed.
She went to the trouble
of running down here to meet me,
and all she got from me
was disappointment!
[KAWASE] Uh, anyway,
we're happy you made it.
Mikazuki, how about it?
[SUBARU] Someone openly talked
about how much
they like my book,
and I can't even respond?
-I...
-[BOTH] I'm sorry.
I'm incredibly
embarrassed, Subaru!
I had no idea
you are who you are,
and I acted like
a complete idiot,
talking about your book
like that!
Huh? Wait.
What is she apologizing for?
That day you came over, I acted
like some literature expert!
And that must have been
so infuriating for you.
[SUBARU] What?
No way. She's got it wrong!
Makes sense. Now that I think
back about that day,
that's why you left.
You were so mad you had
to get out of there, right?
[SUBARU] Not at all! I wish...
I just... I couldn't...
No! I was really happy!
When you guys started talking
that way about my novel,
being so complimentary,
it was a first for me.
And now, you want my autograph?
I'm floored by it all.
But, that day,
it caught me way off guard,
and I just didn't know
how to tell you.
-I'm sorry.
-Huh? What? No way!
You have no reason to apologize!
I get it.
I'm still kind of in shock
right now, honestly.
Look, I haven't the slightest
clue what's going on,
but it seems like
there's some sort of
wonderful coincidence,
yeah?
-Guess so!
-Well...
like the saying goes,
it's a small world, right?
Oh, by the way,
how's Haru's diet going?
It's going really well,
thanks to you.
-Yay, that's wonderful.
-[KAWASE] Haru?
My curiosity
is officially piqued!
What kind of relationship
do they have?
Oh, wow! You don't know
how much this means to me!
And thank you for staying
late on my account!
You've got yourself
two new lifelong fans
in my brother and me!
-Oh. That's nice.
-[NANA] Best of luck!
What? Yeah!
See you around
the neighborhood!
Crap.
I forgot!
I was so shocked I didn't
thank her for coming!
She's pretty far away
at this point.
Oh, well. It's fine.
I can go back to her store
and say thanks there.
I'll do that.
No. That's wrong!
Hey! Okami, hold on!
Thanks!
I'm honored
that you came to meet me!
[giggles]
She heard me.
[KAWASE]
Excellent work, friend.
[SUBARU]
I can't change the past.
There's no reliving the moment
once it's passed you by.
Hope so. It feels good.
Just that...
I was able to get through it.
Thank you.
I couldn't have done it
without you here.
You helped me.
Words can't express
how grateful I am.
I look forward to what
the future holds for us.
If I reach out my hand...
Wow. Thanks, Mikazuki.
[SUBARU]
There's always a chance
someone will be there
waiting there to take it.
I'm just so happy right now.
Hey, come on!
Try to pull yourself together!
[KAWASE]
You're right. Sorry!
[SUBARU]
And when someone is there,
it gives me a courage
I've never known.
If I got through this,
who knows what else I can do?
Or what I could change.
[keys jingling]
I didn't know
I could feel this tired.
All I wanna do is relax.
Wha-- ? What happened?
Did I get robbed? Vandalized?
Wait. Calm down.
Everything's fine.
I don't have anything
worth stealing.
Haru? Haru!
Haru?
[grunting]
-[yelling]
-[thudding]
[SUBARU]
Jeez. Are you okay?
-You're not hurt, are you?
-[yawns]
Thank goodness. Wait.
Should I call the police
and report this?
Why are there tissues strewn
all over the place?
And what's this?
Scratches and bite marks
covering this novel.
What does the forensic
evidence lead us to?
-That the culprit is...
-[trumpet fanfare]
You did this?
You jerk.
Hey, why are you
scooting around like a seal?
[laughs]
How long has it been
since I laughed out loud?
And on my own? No.
I guess I'm not on my own now.
[meows]
What is it?
Does she want more food?
Of course.
It'd be great if I could learn
to understand her better.
It sure would be easier.
[HARU]
Sheesh.
Here I was, worried out
of my mind over this guy
and he just shows up
again like it's nothing.
-[HARU screaming]
-[crashing]
That punk human!
Where is he?
-What could he be doing?
-[scratching]
I can't figure it out!
This awful feeling
isn't going away!
It's driving me crazy!
[frustrated grunts]
Time to hide
in that thing he wears!
Oh, no! It went dark!
Now I can't see anything!
What is going on?
[exhausted panting]
I can't go on.
I'll just rest my eyes.
[HACHI]
Hey, sis, wait up!
[HARU]
Come on, this way.
We have to go
before it starts raining.
You guys stick
close behind me.
[HACHI, SIBLINGS]
Okay!
[HARU]
Kittens? Are you keeping up?
That's right. I don't need
to look back anymore.
It's just me.
No siblings to care for.
Just me.
But that's not entirely true.
Because it isn't just me.
[SUBARU]
Haru.
[HARU]
That's the signal for food.
[SUBARU]
Haru.
[HARU]
And food is important.
[SUBARU]
Haru.
[HARU] No, wait.
That doesn't mean food.
It means something else now.
It belongs to me. It's mine.
[SUBARU grunts]
-[HARU] My special sound.
-Thank goodness.
[HARU]
You seem like you're all right.
-[SUBARU groans]
-[thudding]
[HARU]
No! He's not all right!
This is why I told you
to eat all your food!
What's wrong with you?
[laughing]
[HARU] He's acting even
weirder than usual!
For real. You need to eat food!
Come on, this way.
The food bowl
is over here, remember?
Let's go. Follow me.
[wind rushing]
[HARU] That's it!
Just stick close behind me.
[laughs]
[HARU] I forgot!
I was really hungry, too!
[eager munching]
You better be eating,
human, you hear?
[SUBARU sighs]
Oh, jeez. This mess.
I don't even know where
to begin cleaning it all up.
[HARU] That was yummy!
It's weird, now that I've eaten,
that awful feeling
is totally gone!
I feel great!
Of course!
I didn't feel that way because
the human went away a long time.
It was just because
I was so hungry!
Food really is important, huh?
Good morning, Subaru, buddy!
I brought another batch
of my mom's famous cooking!
Hey, Suba--
Oh, gosh. Subaru?
No. My best friend.
He's... been murdered!
He's in a suit?
Did they dress him up
and kill him?
What am I supposed to do?
Did he leave these weenies
as his dying message?
Weenies. Huh.
What could it mean?
The culprit?
[screaming]
[HIROTO] Haru! Cut it out!
Ah! Come on!
[SUBARU]
Aw, dammit.
Guess I fell asleep
on the floor again.
-[HARU meows]
-[TARO] Flower.
[HARU] Wrong!
Okay, try this. Meow, meow!
-[TARO] Doodle bug.
-[HARU] Wrong again!
[TARO] At this rate,
I'll never learn to speak cat!