♪
[KAWASE]
This is incredible, Mikazuki!
Your signing event last year
was a huge hit,
and our survey says
the readers love you!
My friend,
this year will be massive!
-[SUBARU] Uh-huh.
-On that note,
it’s about time you finally
get started on your next series!
[SUBARU]
My next series.
I have to keep
the ball rolling, huh?
Well, I have been brainstorming
for a while now.
[inhales sharply]
But I can’t come up
with anything!
My mind is blank!
Did I always have those flowers?
[faucet squeaking]
[water spraying]
[SUBARU] It’s been a month now
since Kawase said that to me.
I’ve been racking my brain day
in and out, but...
[sighs]
The assassin cat’s
next mysterious mission. Hmm...
-[spraying]
-[angry meowing]
[HARU hissing]
[SUBARU] A surprise attack
from a new enemy.
A daring escape from danger.
Something relatable
in an extraordinary world.
Something unexpected
in the mundane.
A twist.
-[TARO barking]
-[TANABE] Taro?
My goodness! Watch out!
Subaru!
The hose! Look!
[grunting]
[SUBARU]
I'm so sorry!
I didn’t know
where I was pointing that.
[TANABE chuckles]
Well, I was surprised,
but it’s nothing
to apologize for.
Taro loves a good bath!
-Aw! Yes you do!
-[TARO barks]
Actually, I’m the one who owes
you an apology, if anything.
I already watered
Saho’s garden this morning.
I had no idea you were
going to do it yourself!
I don’t think
I’ve ever seen you
taking care of her
flowers before.
Wait, so you’ve been
looking after the garden
all this time
and I never knew?
I thought they looked awfully
healthy all things considered,
but I’m hardly
a gardening expert.
I was afraid I might be
overstepping my bounds.
But when I was
watering my plants,
I’d lift up the hose and spray!
I should’ve asked
you first, though.
Uh, no. Thank you.
If nobody helped to water them,
they’d be dead.
It's fine.
She took care of that garden
for you, after all.
I didn’t want all her hard work
to go to waste, you know?
[SUBARU]
She did this for me?
Did you see those?
I’m happy to see they’re
blooming again this year.
And there!
Every time you travel,
your garden gets bigger!
You’ll have every flower
in the country soon!
[laughs]
I doubt that!
The lavender I bought in Furano
isn’t even blooming yet!
I’m hoping the blueberries
from Ishikawa
will bear fruit next spring.
So, what are you
planting in that one?
Oh, they’re cute.
Baby Blue Eyes from Ibaraki.
When I saw them,
I knew I had to have them!
Blue is Subaru’s
favorite color, you know.
I would love to show him
a whole field of these,
but I’ll have to settle
for this for the time being.
She used to tell me she hoped
you could enjoy these flowers
from inside the house.
Wherever she went,
she brought back her
favorite plants as a souvenir.
That way, she could
share the world with you.
They were here all this time
and I never knew.
-[TARO barks]
-[TANABE] Okay, okay, Taro!
I'll walk you.
Well, just look at them
from time to time, all right?
They’re so pretty.
And after all,
they were picked out
just for you!
-[TARO barks]
-[TANABE] Hey, don’t run, Taro!
-[TANABE yells, laughs]
-[TARO barks]
♪
[gasps]
[chuckles]
You really outdid yourself, Mom.
But that’s so like you.
Huh?
Guess Haru left.
-[door sliding]
-Haru?
[footsteps]
Where are you?
Did I scare her too much
with that hose?
[gasps softly]
Somebody’s outside.
Why are they just
standing there?
[gasps]
[SUBARU] Maybe they’re trying
to break in!
Haru probably saw them
and went to hide somewhere!
[gasps]
Hi, Mikazuki.
So it’s just you.
Why didn’t you ring
the doorbell, you big weirdo?
[KAWASE]
Uh, well,
there was a young man
here, acting a bit strange,
but he seemed to be on a first
name basis with you.
Where did he go?
Nobody calls me
by my first name.
Only Hiroto.
[KAWASE]
What?
You don’t even
have a cousin
-or something like that?
-[door squeaks open]
If he’s not someone
you know, then...
-Uh-oh...
-[grunting]
-[YUGO] Please, forgive me!
-[KAWASE screaming]
[BOTH whimpering]
Oh, wait. It... it’s you!
Okami’s brother, right?
Yugo, was it?
I'm so sorry.
I knew it might
be kind of awkward
if I just showed up
at your house.
But I had to apologize.
I mean, the way I acted
when we first met...
I grabbed you, said you were
creepin’ on my sister.
-[KAWASE gasping]
-Yeah, but we worked out
the misunderstanding,
so it’s fine.
[YUGO] And I kept talking
about your story,
but I didn’t realize
you were the Mikazuki.
Ever since I found out
who you are,
I’ve been dying
to apologize to you.
But I kept wussing out,
‘cause I was afraid
you might be mad at me.
I thought
you wouldn’t listen.
I didn’t mean for it
to take this long.
I’m sorry, bro.
For real.
No, it wasn’t a big deal
to me, I promise!
[YUGO]
You know,
I really get excited
when I read your stories.
It’s like I’m invincible.
Like anything’s possible.
I wanna work hard,
try new things.
I don't know,
it’s hard to explain,
but your writing
gives me courage.
I’ll always be here
cheering for you.
[SUBARU]
N-no! Please!
I mean, I’m grateful.
Don’t thank me!
It’s nothing!
I owe you for hearing me out!
[YUGO sighs]
Can’t believe
I finally said it.
[SUBARU]
This is new for me.
Feeling joy. Feeling regret.
Being moved by just a few,
simple words.
I don’t know how it happened.
But these days,
all of a sudden,
my heart feels
so much fuller.
When was it
that my life started to change?
[door opens]
[YUGO]
Thanks again for having me, bro.
[KAWASE]
He’s a good kid, isn’t he?
[SUBARU]
Yeah.
Haru seemed to be
awful fond of him, too.
If he’s got some trick,
I sure wish
he’d share it with me, though.
[SUBARU]
Huh? Trick?
I don't know.
Haru seemed to like
Yugo right from the start.
Oh, to be loved!
Oh! By the way,
have any good ideas yet?
-For your new series?
-[SUBARU gasps]
[SUBARU groans]
I, uh, guess that’s a “no.”
I’m sorry.
It seems I’m
suffering from writer’s block.
Listen,
this is just a thought,
but have you
considered traveling?
Maybe for a change
of perspective?
[SUBARU inhales sharply]
No, of course
you haven’t, right?
[SUBARU]
That’s a good idea.
[KAWASE gasps in shock]
Why are you surprised?
It was your suggestion,
wasn’t it?
Well, yes, it was,
but when we first met,
I couldn’t even get you
to come outside.
So this is new!
Sorry, I mean, just tell me
when you decide where to go.
Let me handle it.
I’ll make it happen.
Thanks.
[SUBARU]
Taking a trip, huh?
[food clattering in bowl]
[eager munching]
Okay, but where? [sighs]
[door sliding]
I wonder what happened
with that one.
I don’t think
anything’s ever grown there.
Huh. Guess she did
try to plant something.
-[SUBARU gasping]
-[SUBARU'S MOM] Hey, Subaru.
Next time, maybe we can
all take a trip, together.
See you when we get back!
[SUBARU shuddering]
[KAWASE]
Tokushima?
Shikoku, huh?
That sounds dandy!
I’ll book you a flight
and hotel ASAP!
[SUBARU] Thanks. That’ll save me
a lot of trouble.
I’ve never gone on a trip
like this in my life.
[KAWASE] Hey, no problem.
Happy to help.
Wait!
What are you gonna
do about Haru?
Huh? I’m confused.
[KAWASE]
Well, you’ll be gone.
Don’t you need someone to look
after her till you get back?
[KAWASE]
I didn’t think of that.
[birds chirping]
[SUBARU grumbles]
[inhales sharply]
[NANA]
Going on a trip, huh?
[SUBARU] Yeah. It’s just
two days and one night,
but I’m worried about
leaving her alone.
In that case, it’s probably best
to put her in a pet hotel.
-[SUBARU] Is that a thing?
-Yeah.
I’ll give you the phone number
to a good one, okay?
[SUBARU] First, I gotta
get Haru into the cat carrier.
Haru!
♪
She’s coming!
[SUBARU] Yes! It’s working!
Just like Okami said!
The last time
you used the carrier
was to take her
to the vet, right?
That’s tricky.
She probably won't get inside
on her own after that.
For a lot of cats,
getting in the carrier
means going someplace bad,
so you have to get
a little creative.
Try this.
[SUBARU]
Look, Haru! A treat!
[HARU meows]
[SUBARU] Nailed it!
That was too easy!
Now’s my chance!
-Uh-oh!
-[HARU meowing]
-[SUBARU] Hey! Settle down!
-[HARU meowing angrily]
[angry meowing continues]
Haru?
Hey! You alive?
-Nope. Not gonna work.
-[eager munching]
-[pellets clattering]
-[SUBARU] And stop.
[HIROTO]
Twenty-eight grams?
You sure that’s enough for her?
Uh-huh.
Cats are supposed to eat
several small meals,
so keep it under 35.
Usually three times a day.
I’ll feed her a serving
before I leave.
Try to come by at least
once after that, if you can.
[HIROTO]
No prob.
[pellets clattering]
Looked like
about this much, I think?
[SUBARU]
Wow, how did you pull that off?
[HIROTO] Eh, I used to measure
milk for my sister
when she was a baby.
Stop it!
You just had dinner
a second ago!
For a little cat,
she’s still a big eater, huh?
Yeah, so don’t give her too
much, even if she complains.
She’s still on a diet.
Okay, sure.
I still can’t believe
you’re going on a trip, though.
This is crazy!
You’ll have to hold down
the fort while he’s gone, Haru!
So don’t cry.
You gotta be tough, okay?
[SUBARU gasps]
[laughs quietly]
[phone jingles, vibrates]
It’s Kawase. Hello?
Oh, good. Yeah, thank you.
Uh-huh. Let me write
that down real quick.
Okay, go ahead.
Nagami Hotel.
Pension Iwakuni.
Shijima.
Shijima House?
If you need anything,
the place where we’re
staying is on the fridge, okay?
[crying]
[SUBARU] Shijima House.
I’ll take that one.
Yeah. Yeah. Thanks again.
That where you’re staying?
[SUBARU]
Mm-hmm. Shijima House.
It has to be.
♪
Haru. I’ll see you soon.
[door sliding open,
then closed]
[airplane roaring]
[LADY] We’ve been
expecting you, Mr. Mikazuki!
Here, this is your room.
It’s nice. Thank you.
[LADY]
Um, can I ask you a question?
-Uh-huh?
-It was about three years ago,
but you made a reservation
with us before, didn’t you?
[SUBARU gasps]
[SUBARU]
Yeah, or my parents did.
I thought so.
Your name is so unique.
It stuck with me all this time!
And let’s see...
If I recall correctly,
it was a reservation for three.
For three?
[LADY] We got a call
from the travel agency
at the very last minute,
saying you had canceled.
So, I’m glad you decided to
come back after all this time.
Please enjoy your tea.
[SUBARU]
Mom held out to the very end.
She never gave up on inviting me
till the day they left.
And that trip was the same.
They held that reservation,
hoping I would finally
change my mind.
[SUBARU]
I came here.
But I don’t know
what I hoped to find.
Interested in how
the locals make indigo dye?
A little bit.
You’re famous for it.
In Tokushima, the dye used in
indigo is called “awa-ai."
The process that
craftsmen use to make it
is the same as it
was generations ago.
I didn’t know there were
so many shades of blue.
[LADY] Don’t tell me.
Did you come here because
you’re a blue enthusiast?
[SUBARU]
Uh--
[LADY]
I can’t blame you.
That sweater
does look nice on you.
♪
[inaudible]
[SUBARU'S MOM]
Look at that! I just knew it!
That sweater had your name
written all over it!
Come on.
It’s no big deal.
It is to me.
I picked it out myself,
and you look so handsome in it!
[footsteps]
-[wind whistling]
-[fabric flapping]
[SUBARU'S MOM] My gosh,
you’re wearing that again?
Huh? Why not?
Well, don’t get me wrong,
I’m really happy you like it.
But since you wear it so often,
it’s starting to fade a bit.
-[SUBARU] Is it?
-You didn’t notice?
It was the loveliest color
when we bought it. [gasps]
Hey! Honey, I just
thought of something!
Remember when we went
to Kochi?
[SUBARU]
Mom? Dad?
The place you wanted
to go with me.
The thing you wanted me
to me see.
Was it here?
[crying]
[SUBARU] No matter how much
I think about it,
or how many times I ask,
I’ll never hear their answer.
But I’m here now.
At least I have that.
[SUBARU]
On second thought,
maybe I should have
brought her with me.
Uh--
[HARU] Shoot.
Did I sleep all day again?
[yawning loudly]
Huh? It’s dark,
but he’s still not back yet?
[lapping]
Well, that’s okay.
I’ll keep napping.
He’ll be here by morning.
I bet he’ll be all worked up
about something.
Just like always.
[sniffing]
[yawning loudly]
[LADY] Hmm?
You’re looking for flower seeds?
Uh-huh.
Or a seedling, maybe?
Something this area’s
famous for, if possible.
[LADY] There’s a shopping center
nearby with a nursery.
But it’s in the opposite
direction of the airport
and the weather’s looking bad.
[OLD LADY]
Who needs a nursery?
We’ve got indigo right
in our own back yard.
You just wait there one second.
I’ll go fetch you some.
Uh, are you sure?
[OLD LADY] We’ve got plenty!
No trouble at all!
[door slides open, closed]
Our Indigo should fit the bill,
I’d think.
-Yeah, but...
-It’s fine to take it.
-She’s the owner, after all.
-[SUBARU gasps]
[thunder rumbling]
[OLD LADY] Here you go.
Hope that does it.
Thanks for your trouble.
You're very welcome.
You got that wet
just stepping out?
[OLD LADY]
Oh, yes. Frightful weather.
-[SUBARU] What?
-[rain pouring]
[shudders]
No.
You gotta be kidding.
-[HARU] Nice weather.
-[TARO] It sure is.
[HARU] I wish it would stay
like this all the time.
-[TARO] Me, too.
-[HARU] I guess happiness
is only a sunny day away, huh?