[bell tolls]
[WOMAN]
I heard they were on vacation
and got in a bus accident.
Just think, losing
both parents at once.
The poor boy.
He’s an only child, isn’t he?
Yeah. Poor Subaru.
I hope he’s doing all right.
Subaru?
[SUBARU]
Hmm?
[HIROTO inhales]
[HIROTO sighs sadly]
[indistinct chattering]
[SUBARU] Everything about this
stupid world is annoying.
Here you go. The reference
materials you wanted.
Thanks, I appreciate it.
[KAWASE]
You read more books
than anyone else I know,
Mikazuki.
I don’t know
how you find the time.
So, what do you think?
Are these what you need
to find the inspiration
for your next book?
Who knows. Hope so.
-[GIRL laughing]
-[SUBARU sighs wearily]
Listen, reading’s great,
and all.
But you might find it
more stimulating to go outside,
get some fresh air.
You like this place?
It’s super popular right now.
Busy all the time. Been wanting
to come here for a while
and our meeting
was the perfect excuse--
[SUBARU]
Hey, Kawase.
Did you become my editor
just so you could sabotage
my productivity?
Huh?
This café, it’s filled
with mind numbing people.
And the inane chatter
is driving me crazy!
[chattering in background]
I’ve got to go now.
I'll see you soon.
[KAWASE]
Uh, okay--
Oh. Thanks for bringing me
the books.
[chattering continues]
[chuckling]
What have I gotten myself into?
[KAWASE] Subaru Mikazuki,
acclaimed mystery author.
An eccentric.
Not fond of people.
His previous editor
was put on leave
for a bad case of gastritis.
He’s sensitive.
To be handled with care.
[SUBARU sighs]
[SUBARU] I wish I could live
on a deserted island
and bury myself in books.
Come to think of it,
my parents were always trying
to get me out to see new places.
But, going out means
having to interact with people.
[BOY] Oh, hey.
I’ve read that book before!
Really?
Then, what was it about?
It’s stupid.
The main character’s friend
is the bad guy.
-[SUBARU] Why would he-- ?
-[BOY 2] Wait, for real?
[SUBARU] Shut your mouth!
Shut up! Shut up! Shut up!
Why would someone
take the fun away from me?
I want to find out for myself!
[SUBARU] I don’t need to have
anyone around.
They’d only get in the way.
Mom and Dad,
thankfully, I’ve managed
to pay the bills
just using my imagination.
I hope you know you don’t
have to worry about me.
That’s another reason I’d better
come up with a new story.
Before Kawase gets any more
ideas about taking me out.
Something bit me!
Oh, just a cat.
I thought a zombie had leapt
out of the grave to attack me!
[SUBARU groans]
Now that I’ve gotten
a good look,
its mouth does remind me
a little bit of Mom’s.
Oh, come on. That’s ridiculous.
My mind’s just messing with me.
[SUBARU gasps]
I’ve got an idea
-for my next book!
-[CAT screeches]
[SUBARU] From the shadows.
From the narrowest alleyway.
From beyond the darkness.
I saw those fiercely
glowing eyes,
and I was captivated!
And from then on...
that little cat’s had
a thirst for my blood!
[KAWASE]
Y-ello, Koguma Publishing,
Kawase speaking.
Hey, I got your email.
A mystery about a cat, huh?
That sounds fascinating!
And the cat happens to be
a homicidal maniac? I'm sold.
-[KAWASE laughing]
-Glad to hear it. Thank you.
[KAWASE] So, this is it.
The new hit novel
all your fans
have been waiting for.
I’m gonna need a draft
of the first chapter
by the end of the month.
Think you can manage?
[SUBARU] Yes. I’ve outlined
the whole plot already.
Talk soon.
[SUBARU] It’s got the look
of murder in its eyes!
There's no doubt in my mind.
You’re a killer.
Is it signaling
to its partner in crime?
[barking]
[WOMAN] Stop that barking, Taro.
There’s a good boy.
Oh. Subaru’s out?
No wonder you were barking.
[hissing]
[SUBARU] This must be the path
to its secret hideout.
With one spark of inspiration,
the wings of imagination unfurl!
I can’t believe this.
I never dreamed
anything could inspire me
as much as reading books.
Who would have thought?
-[HIROTO] Hey, Subaru!
-[gasps]
♪
[growls]
Hiroto.
[HIROTO] Don’t you have anything
besides fish sausages here?
[SUBARU growls]
Criticizing my fridge?
Dammit, Hiroto, you can’t just
waltz into someone’s house
unannounced like you
own the place!
And you can’t raid their fridge
without permission, either!
I mean, come on, your parents
live three houses down!
Yeah, about that, you’re never
even going to believe
what happened to me, Subaru.
Check this out.
Some jerk stole my wallet
while I was overseas,
and I still managed
to make it home.
But, then there was a dang fire
on the floor
above me or something,
and my entire apartment
got totally flooded.
I had no money,
I was starving,
and when I went to my parents’
place, they weren’t home.
I’ve had a rough
couple days, man.
Wait, hold on.
I got you this!
I don’t need more crap.
Jeez, dude, sorry.
What is that?
-A cat, what else?
-Yeah, obviously.
I’m not a moron,
but, I mean, why’s it here?
[SUBARU]
I took it in recently.
Wait, you’re keeping it?
You, with a cat?
The guy who doesn’t care about
anything in the world but books?
You okay?
-Will you shut up?
-Wow. Dang.
I’m just shocked.
[SUBARU]
What are you crying about?
I don't know,
I’m just happy for you.
[HIROTO] Hey, kitty.
I’ll bring you a little treat
next time I stop by.
-Be a good kitty for Subaru.
-[hissing]
[SUBARU] Will you just get out
of here and let me work?
[rain pouring]
[cell phone chimes, buzzes]
[KAWASE] Ah, good,
you picked up. It’s Kawase.
Did you get those cat books
I sent over?
[SUBARU] Yeah. I did.
Just now, actually.
[KAWASE] I had no idea
there was so much
reference material about cats.
I’ll be sending you more later.
Oh, fun fact, listen to this.
Did you know that cats can--
[SUBARU] I don’t need any
useless cat facts, thanks.
[KAWASE]
Huh?
That’s a pet peeve of mine.
If I want information,
I can find it myself.
[KAWASE] Oh, right, of course!
Sorry about that.
[SUBARU] Just try to be more
mindful in the future.
[phone disconnects]
[groans]
Were you just talking
to Mikazuki?
Oh, you could tell?
He looks like such a nice kid,
but he’s got a bite.
Boy’s ruthless.
Around here, we call writers
like that one “difficult.”
But he’s a popular author,
so don’t do anything
that might run him off.
[sighs]
Oh, by the way, you might want
to keep a close eye on him
when he’s got deadlines
coming up.
[KAWASE]
Huh?
[SUBARU groans]
[SUBARU] That guy just won’t
leave me alone.
I want to think for myself here.
This is exactly
why I hate people.
[gasps]
♪
[gasps] A spy!
Ow! Dammit! Why is there
cat food on the floor?
-[angry meowing]
-What the hell?
What are you even
trying to do in there?
Whoa, this must be a trap!
I see what’s going on.
It’s a snare to throw the target
off-guard to finish the job!
This is perfect!
You’re pretty cool,
you know that?
You don’t butt into my business
like humans do.
And you stimulate
my imagination.
It’s fantastic.
This is what I get for saying
those words out loud.
I’ve had about enough
of this little stunt.
What the hell, man?
[sighs]
[gasps]
♪
"A tribute to its boss?"
Boss.
I got somethin’ special for you.
[SUBARU] What exactly is it
you expect from me?
I’ll just ignore it.
I’ve got a deadline coming up.
[scratching}
[scratching continues]
[SUBARU] I don’t have time
to mess around.
[cell phone chimes, buzzes]
[meowing]
[SUBARU]
Oh, come on!
I was told no one
would interrupt me!
I told myself lies!
Man. I guess cats are just
as annoying as humans.
Nothing good ever comes
from letting them in!
[sighs]
Okay. Finish line’s in sight.
[rattling]
Ah! Is something trying
to get in and kill me!
Why’d you bring me
your whole dish?
Come on! What is your deal, cat?
Stop interrupting my work!
Crap. Not yet.
I’m not finished.
My manuscript...
It’s useless.
[cell phone chimes, buzzes]
It’s no use. I can’t move.
I’m paralyzed.
[KAWASE]
Mikazuki!
Thank goodness!
I’m glad you’re awake.
[SUBARU] Kawase?
What are you doing here?
Well, you hadn’t answered
my calls in a little while.
So, I freaked out
and came to check on you.
Then, when I got here,
I saw you’d passed out
in the hallway and--
And, uh, I thought you died!
What in the hell
did you do to my window?
I’ve already got someone
coming to replace the glass.
[groaning]
-Hold on. My draft!
-[KAWASE] Right. The ending.
Can we just go
with what’s written here?
[SUBARU]
Huh?
I found your scribblings.
[SUBARU]
I don’t remember writing that.
[KAWASE]
Anyway, someone told me
you forget to eat and sleep
when you’re working.
So, I’m glad I stopped by.
Try not to push yourself
too hard, okay?
[SUBARU] I can’t believe
I had the strength.
[coughs]
I ate cat food, didn’t I?
Uh, Mikazuki?
[SUBARU] Just because it
happened to be in front of me?
Really?
Happened to be?
It couldn’t be
a coincidence, could it?
Listen, Mikazuki.
Maybe you should go
to the doctor.
[SUBARU] No, I’m okay now.
I just needed to rest,
and I hadn’t had anything
to eat in a while.
-You sure?
-[SUBARU] Mm-hmm.
Hey, by the way. Um...
Do you have any idea
what it might mean
if someone keeps bringing their
own food to you, unsolicited?
Hold the phone, Mikazuki.
Are you saying
you have a girlfriend?
You’re already bragging
about her cooking, too!
[SUBARU]
What? No.
But, like...
if someone brings you food,
I think it just means that
they’re concerned about you.
Though, if you really
want to know,
why not skip all the guesswork
and just ask them yourself?
There are some things
you can’t figure out
with imagination alone.
♪
[CAT] I’ve heard legends
about wonderful humans.
They say meeting one can alter
the course of your fate
for the better.
If that's true,
is there a better fate
in store for me with this guy?
He’s been doing
that thing again all day.
I didn’t even know there were
humans who moved so little.
I followed him
because he had food,
but I had no idea
he’d be like this.
[cell phone chimes, buzzes]
[CAT] Although, he hasn’t
done anything mean.
He fills up my food bowl
every day.
And yet, he doesn’t eat
a single bite himself.
[KITTEN]
Sis, I’m really hungry!
[CAT] Doesn’t he know
if you get too hungry, you die?
He shouldn’t mess around!
When I first met him,
he gave me food then, too,
but didn’t take any for himself.
I don’t really get it,
but I’ll never forget what
the tabby who helped me said.
[TABBY] Always repay any favors
done for you!
[CAT]
I live by that.
So, I’m not going nowhere
till I pay him back.
Since he can’t seem
to feed himself,
I’d better give him
some of my food.
-[shrieks]
-[meows]
♪
[CAT] He moved! The human got up
from his spot!
I... I was just
a little surprised
because I wasn’t
expecting it, is all.
[SUBARU]
Ow! Dammit!
[CAT] Go on,
hurry up and eat before--
♪
[shrieks]
[CAT] What are you doing?
Are you stupid?
How dare you waste
perfectly good food like that?
This human is bad!
It’s even worse than I thought!
[CAT groaning]
[SUBARU gasps]
[CAT] Unbelievable!
You’re supposed to eat it!
[meowing]
For me and the rest
of my litter,
just finding enough food
to keep us alive was hard.
Most days we barely ate at all!
I don't know. I guess humans
take food for granted.
I’ll repay the favor,
then split.
♪
[scratching]
[groans, shrieks]
Why won’t you eat,
stupid human?
You’re gonna eat food
and like it!
[straining]
He can’t refuse this!
Oh, finally decided
to come out.
[SUBARU] What the hell?
What is your deal?
[CAT] If you don’t eat,
you won’t be able to move!
That means you can’t get away
if you need to!
Stop interrupting my work--
[thudding]
[CAT] Hey. Human?
Are you all right?
[CAT]
What’s up?
Why won’t you move
or open your eyes?
No!
Come on.
There’s food right here!
You just have to move
your hand a little!
You can eat it all!
I’ve had enough to tide me over!
[meowing]
[crunching]
[CAT]
I did it! He's eating!
Huh?
[scribbling furiously]
[SUBARU]
There! It’s done.
[CAT]
Huh? What just happened?
[snoring]
[CAT]
Is he just sleeping?
Oh, good. He feels warm.
Thank goodness.
What a strange human.
I’m glad he finally left.
[sighs]
[CAT] So, you’re strong enough
to walk now?
It’s you.
Where have you been?
[CAT] I have
repaid your kindness
and cleared my debt.
So, it’s time for me
to leave you now.
Just make sure you eat
enough food, okay, mister?
[shrieks] Hey, man!
You’ve gotta keep it together!
Jeez.
Call yourself a person?
I can’t leave you
alone like this!
[SUBARU] Let’s see.
I thought I still had one left.
[gasps]
But, like...
if someone brings you food,
I think it just means that
they’re concerned about you.
[SUBARU] There’s no way.
A cat wouldn’t do that.
[objects clattering]
[gasps]
Found it.
[CAT] Yes! I had that before,
but only once!
It’s the most delicious
thing ever!
Is he gonna let me have it?
[gasps]
What has gotten into you?
-I don’t understand you at all.
-[CAT] Can I? I’ll be so good!
You're hungry.
So why have you been
giving me all your food?
Do you think...
we’re friends?
[CAT moaning]
[shrieks]
I changed my mind.
I’ll stay with you forever
if you want!
Look.
If you interrupt my work again,
I’ll run you off. You got that?
[CAT]
Tastes so good!
[SUBARU]
A truth.
One that can’t be found
through imagination alone.
What’s that like?
[CAT]
A fateful encounter.
One that brings great changes.
What’s that like?
[SUBARU] I think, a door
to a bright new world...
[BOTH] ...is opening...
a little at a time.
[MAN] I brought you a little
gift to celebrate your new home!
-Yeah, what is it?
-[MAN] A rock.
[WOMAN] Who gives a rock
as a housewarming gift?
[MAN] What, you mean
you don’t like it?
Rocks make excellent gifts!