[SUBARU] Why me?
How did all this happen?
[barking]
[barking, meowing, chirping]
I've clearly made
the worst decision of my life!
[squawking]
[birds chirping]
Hmm.
Hey.
Could you please move?
Why would you sleep
on my laptop, of all places?
I can't get any work
done like this!
Dammit. Guess I'll have
to move you myself.
It's like a barnacle!
Why won't you move?
Oh, I know.
I'll tempt it with cat food.
Well, this sucks.
I forgot I gave it the last
of the food yesterday.
I've gotta have something.
[groans]
I'll order more.
If I do it online...
But I can't!
Oh! I'll just do it
from the browser on my phone.
What? I don't have two
to three business days!
What do I do?
Ugh.
Guess I'll have to go
buy it in person.
No, no, no!
I don't want to go outside,
or worse,
have to deal with people!
But the cat food.
But having to deal
with the outside world!
[groans]
They're out.
Here's what I'll do.
I'll give it bread for now.
Cats eat bread, don't they?
Hang on!
I think I heard somewhere
that it's bad
to give cats human food.
But there was no cat food.
Where else could I buy some?
Is that place a pet store?
What a relief!
I can't believe my luck!
Worst idea ever.
[barking]
I've spent my life
avoiding contact
with any sort
of living thing.
This place is the polar opposite
of everything I believe in.
-[barks]
-[panicked yelling]
[SUBARU grunting, panting]
Get in, get out,
nobody gets hurt.
Cat food!
And more cat food.
So much cat food.
-Which one's right?
-[beeping]
What the heck
is the difference?
[NANA]
You finding everything okay?
Is there something
I can help you with?
Oh, crap!
A human is trying to talk to me!
Um... Um...
I just need cat food.
Great! Shopping for
a little kitty-cat!
I love cats. I'll help you.
What's the name?
[exclaims]
What is this?
Do pet shops require you
to give them your name?
-Subaru Mikazuki.
-Well, that is adorable!
-How demeaning!
-And what about the age?
-Twenty-three years old?
-Wow! Quite the senior citizen!
What kind of world
do we live in that
twenty-somethings
are considered old people?
I wanna go home.
Thanks for being patient
with all the questions.
They just help me narrow down
the options a bit,
to get you the product
fits your needs the best!
-[SUBARU] Huh?
-Here, take these free samples.
You can try them out
before you buy, if you'd like.
I'm sorry.
I have to eat these?
[NANA] Of course not!
They're for Subaru!
Huh?
Wait, I'm confused.
I thought you meant
Subaru was your cat,
but now it seems like...
...that's your name.
And, you're twenty-three?
Oh, I'm sorry!
This is so embarrassing!
I should have been much clearer!
[SUBARU]
I want to disappear.
So, um...
Listen, let's start over.
Want to tell me your cat's name?
[SUBARU]
I haven't given it one.
Oh, really? Well, doesn't that
make things more difficult?
[SUBARU]
I don't think so.
It comes to me
without being called.
Oh, no, I mean,
when you take it to its vet
check-ups and things like that.
Not to mention, you two do live
in the same house, after all.
You two are family.
So, please,
think about giving kitty
a name, okay?
It's for the best.
Oh, also, if it's young,
this food will be
a better choice for it.
Okay?
[SUBARU]
Yeah. I have to go!
Thanks, and good luck
with everything.
Hi. It's your favorite
editor, Kawase.
Sorry to bug you,
but can you chat for a sec?
[SUBARU panting]
[SUBARU]
Yes. What is it?
What's happening now?
Are you all right?
[panting]
Yes. I'm fine. What's up?
[KAWASE]
Oh. Good. Uh...
It's nothing urgent, really,
I just wanted to let you know.
Um, the response
to your new book has been great!
I just couldn't wait
to tell you.
Oh. I see.
[KAWASE]
Uh, by the way, Mikazuki,
have you thought of a name
for the cat yet?
[SUBARU]
What the hell?
Everyone's on my case
about that!
Why do I have to
give it a name at all?
[KAWASE] Uh, look, man,
you sure there's nothing wrong?
Please calm down.
[KAWASE]
Hey. Mikazuki?
[SUBARU] I should have just
ordered it online
like I wanted to.
Then I wouldn't have had
to go out in public.
And this wouldn't
have happened.
[KAWASE]
Uh, anyway,
we've gotten lots
of fan letters.
Everybody's dying to know
what the cat's name is.
[SUBARU]
Oh, wait.
He was talking about
the cat in the story?
-[KAWASE] You still there?
-[SUBARU] I'm listening.
[KAWASE] Giving the cat a name
would definitely make readers
feel more attached to it.
So, just give it
some thought, okay?
Yeah, sure.
A name, huh?
[HIROTO] Yo, Subaru!
Are you at home?
-Well, that's rare.
-[barking]
Hey, Taro.
Are you being a good boy?
There we go.
Seriously, does this guy
ever shop? Oh!
That should do it. Good.
Mom always cooks too much.
Subaru should be all set
for a while with this, though.
-Oh! Oh!
-[hissing]
What?
Hey! Come back!
Hmm.
Man, what was
the cat's name again?
Meh, whatever.
I'll ask Subaru next time.
[birds chirping]
[SUBARU]
I get that fans ask questions.
But, still...
[WOMAN]
Hi, Koro. How are you today?
[dog barking]
She's always so spirited!
That's the truth.
Sometimes I wish she could be
as quiet as her sister, Berry.
[SUBARU]
The harsh reality is...
I don't have anybody
to call by name anymore.
I'd prefer not to talk
to anyone, though, honestly.
And calling out to a creature
that can't understand me...
[BOY]
Go get it, Ryutaro!
[BOY laughs]
Over here!
What's the point?
All right! You're the best dog
in the world, Ryutaro!
[laughing]
-Okay, let's go home!
-[barking]
[door closes]
It's gone. Where'd it go?
Oh, well.
Time to get to work.
[scratching]
[panting]
[typing]
I thought I had some other
reference books over here.
[hissing]
How can anything sleep
in such a tight space?
What are you even thinking, cat?
Come on.
A name, huh?
I don't see how giving you one
would change anything.
Maybe thinking of a name
for my character will help.
I might stumble
across one for you, too.
That said, I'm a writer.
I can't just throw names
around arbitrarily
without giving them
serious thought.
Each name has to represent
the individual.
It has to fit their personality.
A cat's personality?
It's just a cat.
It's no use! I got nothing!
Hold on.
Why don't I just let it
choose its own name?
I'll see if it responds
to anything.
A... Amane.
E... Enishi.
I... Iroha.
U... Uguisu.
Ogi?
Kasane. Kinu.
Kurumi. Keshi.
Ryu. Ruri.
Not a single response.
What the heck am I doing?
This is stupid.
-Wakaba--
-[thwacking]
[SUBARU grunts]
I'm an idiot.
I'm getting nowhere.
Which tells me something.
Neither people nor animals
want anything to do with me.
Hey, Mom! Mom!
Will you read this?
[SUBARU'S MOM] Oh, again?
You must really love this book.
"Then the crescent moon said,
"'It looks like
the sun is awake.
'So, it's time for me
go to sleep.'"
Crescent moon?
Isn't that what our name means?
[SUBARU'S MOM laughs]
That's right.
Yeah, but, the crescent
moon went to sleep.
I want the crescent moon to be
up in the sky all the time.
Really? But you sleep
at night, too, don't you?
Well, the moon has to sleep.
The moon's out at night,
and the sun's out all day.
They like to work together,
to light the whole world's way.
[SUBARU]
Are the sun and moon friends?
[SUBARU'S MOM]
Of course. Very good friends.
And they're important
to each other.
The sun in spring.
Spring. “Haru.”
Haru.
Haru?
[meows]
Wait.
Did it just respond to that?
“Haru”?
Crap! The food!
I completely forgot
about feeding it!
Thank goodness
for free samples.
I'm awful.
What kind of owner deprives
his cat of food like that?
I told you.
We don't have any more of that.
I'll go buy some.
But you'll have to wait.
So, just hang out here
and be good.
-Haru.
-[meows]
It's not like the cat
can understand me, right?
I must be losing my mind.
Talking to a cat.
I mean, who does that?
[NANA] You two do live
in the same house, after all.
You two are family.
[HARU] “Haru."
I know that word. I like it.
It sounds so nice and warm.
I've made a great discovery.
I love lying in this spot.
It always feels
so cozy right here.
I think it's my favorite place,
especially for taking naps.
[gasps]
What's this?
What's going on?
I found this spot first,
stinky human.
Leave me alone!
I'm never gonna let you have it!
Ha. I won.
-[barking outside]
-[door rattling]
What is that?
It's so loud.
Aw, this thing this gets cold
fast when it makes that noise.
But that's fine.
I was getting hungry, anyway.
I love this life.
I can eat whenever
I start feeling hungry now!
This is the best!
No food?
-[HIROTO] Seriously...
-[HARU] Wh-- What's that?
[HIROTO]
Oh!
Mom always cooks too much.
Subaru should be all set
for a while with this, though.
Oh! Oh!
Oh, no!
[panicked screaming]
Why was he here?
He's always eating!
Did he eat all my food, too?
I got careless.
I was dumb to assume
I could eat whenever I wanted.
Took it for granted that
there'd always be food for me.
I should've known.
But, now it's gone.
I'm so hungry.
[GIRL] Hi, kitty!
I was hoping I'd see you again!
Wait here. I'll be right back!
-Here you go!
-[HARU whimpering]
Make sure it's not
too hot to eat.
-Haru.
-Sure seems cool enough to me.
[GIRL] Doesn't Haru's mom
make the tastiest food?
-[HARU] Haru?
-[GIRL] I love her cooking, too!
-[HARU] Does “Haru” mean “food”?
-You know what?
Watching the kitty eat is
making me want something, too!
What am I going
to do with you?
[HARU] Haru. Haru.
I like it.
It sounds so nice and warm.
-[shrieking]
-[SUBARU gasps]
That scared me!
What's your problem?
Why do you want
to take my spots?
Well, you can't have
this one, either!
-[SUBARU] Ryu. Ruri.
-[HARU] Ugh.
What's that human
mumbling about over there?
-[SUBARU] Wakaba.
-[HARU] Shut up!
Hey, that worked.
Now it's peaceful and quiet.
-What a relief.
-[SUBARU] Haru. Haru.
Hey, it's that word.
The one with the warm sounds.
Haru?
Food! Ah!
Ah!
He's got it!
Food! Food!
[eager whimpering]
I knew it!
It does mean “food”!
[puzzled whimpers]
Gone already?
Hey, human!
There's no more food!
Can you bring me some more?
Please?
Okay. So just hang out here
and be good, Haru.
Yeah! “Haru.”
Haru's what I want!
[meows]
I know what that word means!
It means that food
is coming, right?
[bell tolls]
What? Where'd he-- ?
Where's the... food?
I don't understand.
Why is that human so confusing?
[SUBARU]
Hey. Where'd you go?
I got you some more food.
-Haru!
-[food clinking in bowl]
[HARU]
Food! More food!
[WOMAN ON TV] My shoulders,
they've been so tight lately.
I know what you need!
Stick on one of these!
Haru Stick-Ons!
Ow, my sciatica.
-[MAN ON TV] Slap it on! Haru!
-[HARU yells]
-[MAN ON TV] Haru Stick-Ons!
-Where's the food?
-What's the matter with you?
-Food!
[MAN 2] Hey, can you say
“Haru” ten times, fast?
[WOMAN 2]
Haru, Haru, Haru, Haru, Haru,
Haru, Haru, Haru,
Haru, Haru!
-That made me hungry.
-[MAN 2] Yeah, same here.