[SUBARU] An old house, bearing
no outward signs of life,
when the shadow
of a visitor approaches.
[NANA]
Hello?
[SUBARU gulps]
-[SUBARU] Who could it be?
-[NANA] It’s Okami.
[WOLF howls]
[SUBARU]
Here you go.
Sheesh. That kind of thing
never happens in real life,
just in dumb mystery novels!
Tea sounds so nice.
Thank you.
And I’m sorry.
I’m kind of embarrassed.
It just occurred to me
that I haven't
officially introduced
myself to you!
So, we should fix that!
I’ll start.
My name is Nana Okami.
Nice to meet you.
Now that that’s out of the way,
what exactly is it
that brings you over here?
Oh, my goodness,
this must be Haru!
Hi, kitty!
Wow, she’s not nearly
as fat as I expected!
You’ll get her down
to a normal weight in no time.
I hope you’re right
about that.
I think she’s gotten fat
because there’s something wrong
with the way
I’ve been feeding her.
Huh, interesting.
Well, if you wouldn’t mind,
maybe you could show me
how you normally feed her.
[SUBARU]
Normally?
-[food bag rustling]
-[pellets clattering in bowl]
[SUBARU]
Normal.
[concerned whimpering]
Uh...
[whimpering continues]
-That's way too much!
-[SUBARU gasps]
[NANA]
I'm sorry.
It was just so much more
than I thought it’d be.
So, I flipped out.
She’s always eaten
every bit of her food.
I assumed it was right.
[NANA]
A cat with a big appetite
will eat everything
you put in their bowl.
Let me show you how much
a cat Haru’s size needs to eat.
I think it’ll surprise you.
You’ll need to feed her
two meals per day
of the same amount.
[SUBARU]
That’s nothing!
Oh. I’ll keep that in mind.
From now on
that’s what she gets.
Well. Hold on.
Abrupt changes in her diet,
can end up causing stress,
and that’s unhealthy.
Make sure she’s
getting lots of exercise,
and gradually less food
every day,
to keep from upsetting her.
To get her moving,
you can give
her one of these to play with.
But isn’t that
just a water bottle?
[NANA] Yep, but you cut a hole
in it that’s only big enough
for one piece of food
to get through.
Why don’t I show you
how it works?
Here, Haru! Get it!
[NANA] She’ll realize that
she has to roll it around
quite a bit
to get the food to come out.
I see.
Seems like fun.
[NANA] Eating too fast
is one cause of obesity.
If you trick them into taking
a little more time
to eat their food,
it makes them feel full faster,
and it’s a great form
of exercise
that utilizes
their hunters’ instincts.
[SUBARU]
That works like a charm.
Amazing.
I never would have come up with
something like that on my own.
Haru seems like
a naturally active cat,
so I’m sure she’ll
slim down in no time.
But my cat hates exercising,
which made things harder.
[SUBARU]
Oh, really?
[NANA] Here’s a picture of him
when he was at his fattest.
[SUBARU]
Buddha cat!
Wow.
He looks like
a furry basketball.
I used to spoil him
a little too much.
But then, look.
Here’s what he looks like now.
[SUBARU]
Whoa.
Oh. So, you have two cats?
[NANA]
Yeah.
The little one’s name is Hachi.
And the one who used
to be fat is Roku.
[SUBARU]
His pose.
Haru does that a lot, too.
[NANA] Roku is three years old,
and Hachi’s still a kitten,
a little under six months,
I think.
It’s funny. They both sort
of bear a resemblance.
Well, to you, I think.
[gasps] Do you really think so?
No one’s ever
said that before.
But I have heard
that your mannerisms
and looks start to become
more similar with time,
when you’re a family.
[SUBARU'S MOM]
Hey, sweetheart? And Subaru.
[laughs]
Oh, gosh!
You two become more
and more alike every day!
Yeah, I’ve heard that, too.
♪
[SUBARU] Come to think of it,
Mom loved animals, too.
If she... were still alive...
Family, huh?
And Haru.
She had a family
at some point, too.
I wonder if she misses
them sometimes,
and wishes she could
see them again.
Thank you for all
your help today.
You’re welcome!
If you have any other questions
about this stuff,
you know where to find me,
so feel free
to drop by whenever!
[SUBARU gasps]
[SUBARU] Wait, is that-- ?
That’s her key!
[HARU hisses]
Don’t hiss at me. Come on.
That’s not yours, let it go.
[SUBARU grunting]
Let go!
Oh, no, her claw’s stuck in it.
[HARU hisses]
It’s probably
her house key, too!
And I don’t have her number.
It’s only been
a few minutes.
She couldn’t have
gotten too far.
I need to calm down.
She’ll come back
when she notices it’s missing.
I don’t need to chase after her.
We neighbors have to look out
for each other, you know?
[gasps]
[SUBARU]
Let’s go. There’s still time!
It’s her!
Hey! Okami, wait!
Oh, hi, Subaru. Uh,
is something the matter?
You left this.
I did? That’s my house key!
But why did you
bring Haru with you?
Oh. Her claw is really
stuck in there, huh?
It’s probably safer
if we just cut it,
rather than try
to pull it off.
I have special scissors.
I’ll go get them right now.
Wait here,
I’ll be right back!
Well, I would, but,
how are you going to get in?
Oh, right. I can’t, can I?
I’m sorry about this, Haru.
Uh, hold on while I look
for the safety scissors.
You’re welcome to wait inside,
if you’d rather.
Uh, no, I’ll wait
out here, thanks.
[SUBARU gasping]
-Hey, wait!
-[NANA] Hachi, Roku, I’m home!
[SUBARU] When you get involved
with people,
sometimes things
go in directions
you never would have expected.
And this is... a prime example!
Haru, what are you doing?
Leave that cat alone!
-Haru!
-[meowing]
[SUBARU] You can’t just bite
someone else’s cat!
Haru!
-[thudding]
-[grunting]
Thank goodness!
At least the other cat
doesn’t seem to be hurt.
Now’s my chance!
Come on, get over here!
Haru!
[groans]
I must’ve been crazy.
There’s no way a human
and an animal
can really
understand each other.
[NANA]
Hey, Subaru. I’m sorry,
but I can’t find
the safety scissors anywhere.
Huh?
I thought I heard a commotion,
but those two seem to be
getting along great!
[SUBARU] Please, get Haru away
from your cat, quickly!
I’m afraid she’ll hurt him.
She bit his neck a minute ago!
I’m so sorry!
[NANA]
Oh. I think everything’s fine.
Hachi isn’t acting at all like
he’s scared or in pain.
I’m sure she was just
putting him his place.
He gets a little
too rambunctious sometimes.
I see. She disciplined him.
Hachi! Come here!
[SUBARU]
Huh?
[meows]
[NANA] You’re in a good mood,
aren’t you?
Did you make a new kitty friend?
Of course you’re happy.
[SUBARU gasping]
He... he just comes to you
when you call him?
Huh?
[SUBARU]
I call Haru, but she...
looks at me like I’m nothing.
[NANA] Aw. Well, look,
a lot of that just depends
on the individual
cat’s personality!
Do you use her name
often at home?
Like, do you talk
to her and stuff?
I mean, not really.
I say her name when I feed her.
And then when I feed her again,
and again.
Now that I think about it,
I have my doubts
that she actually understands
anything I say
to her at all.
Technically, no.
Animals don’t understand
our language, per se.
That makes it pretty difficult
to communicate with them,
doesn’t it?
It’s hard, but you can.
Instead of using words,
you have to come up with other
ways to convey your feelings.
And don’t worry.
Whether they understand or not,
I think what’s important
is that they know
you’re trying to communicate.
[SUBARU]
Easy for you to say.
But I’ve been calling her
since we got here.
-[TEACHER] Mikazuki!
-[SUBARU gasps]
[TEACHER]
You’re here by yourself again?
Why don’t we go find some
friends for you to play with?
I’ll go with you, okay?
Now, come on!
[SUBARU]
Forcing things like that
never moves anyone’s heart.
I should know
that better than anyone.
Haru.
Uh, come here.
[gasps lightly]
-[light footsteps]
-[keys jangling]
[SUBARU gasps]
[meows]
[SUBARU]
All those times I called you,
you never came.
What the heck?
Silly cat.
Haru.
[HARU]
What’s going on?
I’m not sure I understand,
but it’s nice.
♪
This house sure has been
awfully busy lately.
Now there’s another human here
who I don’t know.
I hope this one isn’t
as annoying as the others.
That guy’s not too terrible,
but that other one?
Hmm.
Well, since my human is
just sitting there, spacing out,
I’ll have to judge
this one for myself!
-[NANA] Hi, kitty!
-[HARU groans]
[NANA] Wow, she’s not nearly
as fat as I expected!
You’ll get her down
to a normal weight in no time.
[HARU]
She’s not trying to grab me.
But still, I can’t let
my guard down yet.
-[pellets clattering in bowl]
-[HARU gasps]
[HARU]
I know that sound! And smell!
It’s food!
She’s always eaten
every bit of her food.
I assumed it was right.
[HARU] I know my food is up
there on top of this thing!
But why is he guarding it
more than usual?
[NANA]
Here, Haru!
[HARU]
That’s the signal!
-[NANA] Get it!
-[HARU moans]
[HARU] Oh, look!
There’s the food!
Huh? It’s there,
but I can’t get into it.
-Hey, you! Stop right there!
-I see.
That seems like fun.
[HARU groaning]
[HARU]
Hold it, so I can get the food!
Ha ha!
[satisfied munching]
Tasty!
The rest of you don’t
stand a chance.
You’re mine! [snickers]
Ha!
Ha ha!
[sighs contentedly]
I’m already full.
[contented sighing]
Huh?
[HARU]
This human.
There’s something different
about her.
I’ve never seen her before.
But all this feels
kind of familiar somehow.
[NANA] If you have any other
questions about this stuff,
you know where to find me,
so feel free
to drop by whenever!
[HARU]
Ah, that was so much fun.
[groaning]
What’s this thing?
Fluffy.
[sniffing]
I know this smell!
[gasps] Wait, is that... ?
That’s her key!
[HARU]
Huh? No, it’s mine!
-[HARU shrieks]
-[SUBARU] Don’t hiss at me.
[HARU]
No way!
[SUBARU] Come on.
That’s not yours. Let it go.
[HARU] You can’t have it!
The smell! I know it!
Wha-- ?
[NANA] I’m sorry you had
to come all this way.
Here it is.
I’m sorry about this, Haru.
[HARU] No! Stop!
I won’t let you have it!
[HARU straining]
Hold on while I look
for the safety scissors.
You’re welcome to wait inside,
if you’d rather.
[HARU]
It’s that smell again.
[NANA]
Hachi, Roku, I’m home!
[SUBARU]
Hey, wait!
[HARU]
I remember now.
[HACHI gasps]
-[HACHI] Big Sis?
-[HARU gasps]
[HARU]
I can’t believe it.
I thought
I’d never see him again.
[HACHI gasping]
[HACHI]
It is you. Isn't it?
Sister!
[HARU groaning]
-[HACHI] I missed you so much!
-[HARU] Hey! Stop it!
-[tussling]
-[grunting]
-[HACHI] Sister! Sister!
-[HARU exclaims]
-[tussling]
-[HARU huffs]
[HARU]
Just calm down, would you? Ha!
-[HACHI] Okay, I'm sorry!
-[SUBARU yells]
[HACHI whimpers]
[HARU gasps]
[HARU]
He feels so warm.
[HACHI]
Hmm?
Sis?
[HARU]
I’m so happy you’re okay!
[HACHI] Yeah!
I’ve been doing really good!
[laughs]
Oh, yeah. Remember?
That day...
Those scary flying
things came back.
We ran away
from them really fast,
just like we promised
you we would.
We kept running
so they wouldn’t catch us.
But the next thing I knew,
we got split up.
I was really scared, so I...
I just ran away by myself.
[whimpers]
[HARU]
I’m sure it was scary for you.
But you tried your best!
I’m really proud of you.
[HACHI laughs]
[HACHI]
Hey, Sis. Come here.
[HARU]
Hmm?
[HACHI]
That lady there’s named Nana.
She saved me.
She’s really nice!
[HARU]
That human saved you?
[HACHI] She gives me food!
And plays with me, too!
[HARU gasps]
[HACHI]
Big Sister, give me a bath!
[HARU]
Honestly,
you’re still as spoiled
as you always were.
[HACHI]
Hey, Big Sis! Give me a bath!
[SIBLING]
Yeah, me, too! Me, too!
[HARU]
His fur’s shiny.
[HACHI]
Sister?
[HARU] Guess he’s going
to be all right now.
He doesn’t need me
to protect him.
[HACHI]
Big Sis?
[HARU] I’m glad that you found
such a nice human.
[SUBARU] Haru--
[grunts]
[HARU] Jeez, what the heck’s
the matter with you today?
This is no time
for food right now!
[HACHI] Food?
What about food?
[HARU] That word he said
means food, doesn’t it?
[HACHI]
I’m not really sure,
but I don’t think
it means that.
Because, look at his face.
He’s watching you
really closely.
I think that word means
he’s trying to call for you.
[HARU]
Call for me?
But why would he do that?
Am I supposed to go to him
when he calls me?
[HACHI] Yeah, and when you want
to call me, I have a new word!
-It’s Hachi! Like it?
-[HARU] Hachi?
[HACHI] That lady, Nana,
told me it’s my name!
It’s a special word
that’s just for me!
Awesome, huh?
When Nana calls,
we go to her,
and it makes her really happy!
So it makes me happy, too!
[NANA]
Hachi! Come here!
[HACHI]
Look! She’s calling me now!
I’ll be right back, okay?
[HACHI laughing]
[HARU]
He's happy?
But, I never thought
about going to the human
for anything but food before.
What should I do?
I’m confused.
But I guess...
[SUBARU]
Haru.
[HARU]
Hmm?
Uh... come here.
[HARU]
What's this?
Do those arms mean
he wants me to go to him?
But he seems all right,
not like he’s in any trouble.
♪
What is it? [gasps]
All I did was come over.
What's going on?
Is he happy?
[SUBARU]
Haru.
[HARU] A special word
that’s just for me?
Humans are weird.
[HACHI] Haru, huh? Is that the
name your human gave you?
[HARU whimpers]
-[kicking]
-[SUBARU yells]
Oh, no, Subaru!
[SUBARU] When you get
involved with people,
sometimes things go
in directions
you never would have expected.
[HARU]
Just so you know, this guy
would be
hopeless without me,
I’m his protector!
He needs me to stay close
and keep an eye on him!
That’s all! Okay?
[HACHI]
You’re so big and strong!
You’re not hurt badly,
are you?
[SUBARU]
For example...
No. I’m all right.
[grunts]
[SUBARU]
I never expected this.
The hell?
What’s going on between
you and Nana, bro?
Hey! I asked you
a freakin’ question!
[HACHI]
This guy’s named Roku.
-[MAN] Hello?
-[ROKU] Who might you be?
[HARU]
I'm Hachi's big sister.
Thanks for taking care
of my baby brother!
[HACHI] What kind of stuff
do you dream about, Roku?
[ROKU]
I dream of a paradise
with endless fields
of delicious,
fluffy bonito flakes.
[HACHI]
Wow, that’s awesome!