[birds chirping]
[KAWASE] Are you excited
about your first volume
having a release date?
Here's some ideas for the cover.
What are your thoughts?
A lot of your readers
are teenagers and young adults,
so, maybe a bright,
fun design would be good.
Then again,
this one is pretty hard-hitting,
and fits the tone
of the story.
Oh, wait,
on second thought,
I think this one
is my personal favorite.
Man, it's hard to choose
just one!
Is it, though?
[SUBARU] Most things in life are
pointless to stress out over.
As for me, I just want to live
a quiet life,
and avoid making
any unnecessary waves.
Okay, so, there was one
other marketing-related thing
I wanted to run by you.
A book-signing
to commemorate the release.
[gasps]
The sales department
and affiliated bookstores
are really pushing for it.
They think a signing
could boost sales
and create buzz for the release,
so, uh--
-I refuse.
-Huh?
And that's the final word.
[SUBARU] A book signing
is totally out of the question.
I make it a point to avoid
any situation I can't control!
Yeah, to be honest,
I knew even before I asked
that your answer would be
something along those lines.
All right, then.
I'll try to break the news
gently to sales and marketing.
[doorbell rings]
-Are you gonna answer that?
-Probably a solicitor.
-Right, but still...
-[ringing intensifies]
[SUBARU]
They'll go away.
Look, why don't I just politely
send them away for you?
-Huh?
-[ringing continues]
Sure, if you want.
[SUBARU] But sometimes, the ones
who can't be controlled...
Hey! What's up, Subaru?
[gasps]
Turned out to be Hiroto!
Can we stay a while?
[SUBARU] Will attack if you
let your guard down!
[SUBARU]
He brought kids?
Go on, you three.
Say hello to Mr. Subaru.
[KIDS]
Okay!
Nice to meet you!
I'm Hayato Yasaka
and I'm in the third grade!
My name's Narumi.
And I'm also in the third grade!
[TWINS giggle]
As you can probably already
tell, these two are twins.
And this cutie...
Misora. I'm three!
Very good!
You know how to say
how old you are!
-We know how, too!
-So, um...
Our parents had to
go out of town on short notice.
They'll be gone overnight,
and I got stuck with the runts.
Of course, I had to leave work
early to look after them.
When I mentioned Haru,
they had to meet her.
I'm used to you showing up
unannounced, but this is...
Oh, yeah. You haven't met
the runts before, have you?
[nervously exhales]
-[SUBARU] Who's that?
-[HIROTO] Huh?
Oh, that's right.
You met Nagisa, yeah?
But it's been forever.
[YOUNG NAGISA]
Big brother!
♪
[YOUNG NAGISA]
Brother!
[YOUNG SUBARU]
Huh?
[YOUNG HIROTO]
I told you, no girls allowed!
But why?
I wanna come
with you guys, too!
-Oh.
-Nice to see you again.
Sorry we all just barged in
on you like this.
-Um...
-Where's Haru at?
Can we go see her?
Uh, she's around here
somewhere.
[HAYATO]
All right! Operation Find Haru!
[NARUMI, MISORA]
Yeah!
Where do you think she's hiding?
[MISORA]
I wanna go pet Haru right now!
Right!
Initiate Operation Find Haru!
[ALL]
Yeah!
[SUBARU]
But, Kawase...
[KAWASE moans]
[NARUMI]
Yay! I just saw Haru!
[HAYATO]
She's over there! She ran away!
[NARUMI]
Hold on! Aw, she's so cute!
[HIROTO]
Hey, don't. Be gentle with her.
Uh, Kawase...
What is it?
[KAWASE]
I can't stand it!
Those kids get to play
with my sweet Haru,
while I'm stuck in here
adulting with this guy!
Why don't we take
a little break?
[KAWASE]
Okay! Haru-meow!
[sighs]
I guess I'll put
some coffee on.
[gasps]
Oh, Subaru.
Nothing in your fridge
as usual, I see.
[SUBARU]
Didn't your mom teach you
it's rude to raid
other people's fridges?
Yeah, but I'm not.
This is just an inspection.
I'm making sure
you're eating right.
[stomach rumbles]
I ate... yesterday?
I think.
Dude. You should eat every day.
Jeez.
Ah, takeout, huh?
Listen.
Can I order delivery
from this place?
It'll be on me, of course.
Yeah?
[stomach rumbles]
Sure. I guess.
-Kitty!
-Cuteness overload!
Be gentle, Misora.
-Hurry! I wanna hold Haru next!
-Then it's my turn!
Hey! Misora, over here!
Hey, runts. You guys
feel like some take-out?
We're eating
at Subaru's tonight!
-Wow, really?
-Awesome!
Um, Kawase,
you're welcome to join.
Look, "crap" omelet!
[laughing] Crab omelet, huh?
Excellent choice!
Yeah, that's what I want, too!
-[TWINS giggling]
-[SUBARU sighs]
[SUBARU]
I'll have ramen.
Guess I'll go get
everything ready.
Gotcha.
[SUBARU sighs]
[SUBARU]
Give me a friggin' break!
I don't even have
the faintest idea
how I'm supposed
interact with kids!
And I don't think
there have ever been
this many people
in this house at once!
Maybe not even total.
Oh, crap!
Do I have enough teacups
for everyone here?
[sighs]
Excuse me.
Do you, um,
need any help in here?
-I'm a little bored.
-Huh? Well...
We might need some paper cups.
[SUBARU'S MOM]
Look at this, Subaru!
I found this lovely tea
set on our trip!
It was so beautiful,
I just couldn't resist!
[BOTH chuckle lightly]
Won't it be nice
when we have lots of visitors?
Maybe we can host a party!
Will that ever happen?
Oh, quiet, of course it will!
Please.
I can't wait until
we get to use it together.
[laughs]
[gasps softly]
Found it.
[paper rustling]
Um, I don't think
I've ever known someone
who had as many books as you.
One, two, three, four...
I guess I like to read.
Uh, yeah. So do I.
I'm the student librarian
at my school.
It's actually
Reading Week right now.
I'm making a list
of suggested books.
[SUBARU] Wait, maybe barley tea
would be better.
[NAGISA]
Are there any books
you could maybe recommend,
Subaru?
[SUBARU] "Books I'd like
to recommend?"
[YUGO] Actually,
there's a story in here
about a cat you might like.
[SUBARU]
I never imagined I'd be asked
to make a book
recommendation!
There's no way I could narrow
down my favorites to just one!
And I could never explain
what makes each one great
in just a few words!
What do I do?
Besides, she's a girl,
and way younger than me.
I have no idea what kind
of books she'd be into!
How can I make
a good recommendation?
What am I supposed to say?
I can't do it!
I'm freaking out!
Sorry. Excuse me.
Was it too soon?
Maybe I was too familiar.
-[SUBARU] Here.
-[NAGISA gasps]
[SUBARU] This book is one
of my all-time favorites.
I was really into it
when I was your age.
[chuckles]
Sure you don't mind
if I borrow it?
Uh, no.
Just bring it back
whenever you're done.
[SUBARU]
Did I do it right?
Is this how you're supposed
to make a recommendation?
Thank you!
I can't wait to dive into it!
[SUBARU]
I guess I did.
[doorbell rings]
[WOMAN]
Delivery!
[TWINS]
Wow! It looks yummy!
[ALL]
Thank you for the food!
Eat food!
Mm! Delicious!
"Crap" omelets are the best!
It's "crab omelet."
[meows]
[ALL laughing]
[HAYATO]
Wow! The ramen looks good, too!
Yeah, it does!
-Uh, you guys wanna try it?
-[BOTH] Yeah!
-I want some, too!
-[meows]
Mm!
This is the best thing ever!
[meowing]
[ALL]
Thanks for the tasty meal!
[MISORA]
Yummy!
[sighs]
[SUBARU]
It's finally over.
Peace and quiet at last.
[NARUMI] Everybody who wants
to play hide and seek,
touch my finger!
[ALL]
I do!
[SUBARU moans]
[KAWASE]
Everybody hidden?
[KIDS laughing]
You'll never find us!
Oh!
[gasps]
[MISORA]
Shh!
[KAWASE]
Ready or not!
[TWINS]
You'll never find us!
[BOTH]
Shh!
Are you ready?
‘Cause here I come!
[BOTH giggling]
[KAWASE] Now where could
those kids be hiding?
Hmm.
Could they be in here?
-[MISORA giggles]
-[KAWASE] Hmm?
What's this, now?
Really? Nobody in here?
Hey, guys! Where did you go?
[TWINS]
Time for a staring contest!
[BOTH exclaiming]
[TWINS exclaiming]
-[BOTH giggling]
-Man, he's good!
Mr. Subaru,
you're a really good starer!
[MISORA laughing]
[HAYATO] Mr. Subaru,
come look at this!
[NARUMI]
Come see how cute Haru is!
[KAWASE]
You are gonna love it!
[GROUP laughing]
[barking]
Oh, what's going on
over there?
Does he have visitors?
Well. Sounds like they're
having a nice time.
-[chuckles]
-[barks]
[HIROTO]
Hayato. Narumi.
Come on,
it's time to go home.
[KAWASE chuckling]
Look at Misora.
She's fast asleep.
Haru must be
hiding somewhere.
Yeah, and I wanted
to hold her one last time
before we had to go home.
You held her
enough for one day.
Subaru, thanks
for having us over.
Yeah, thanks for
putting up with us.
I'm exhausted.
[TWINS giggling]
-Didn't you have fun today?
-[HIROTO laughing]
Next time we come over,
I'll bring you
some of Mom's
cooking to say thanks.
Gotta say, these runts
seem to like you.
Let's play again soon,
Mr. Subaru. Okay?
Yeah, next time we'll bring
our friends from class!
[SUBARU]
Ah... Uh-huh.
Well, then, Mikazuki,
see you tomorrow!
[HAYATO]
Aw, no fair!
[NARUMI]
I'm coming over tomorrow, too!
[HIROTO]
Hey, take it easy.
Let's not impose
on Mr. Subaru.
[sighs]
I'll never get
used to people.
[groaning]
Guess you had a pretty
rough day, too, didn't you?
[gasps]
[HARU snoring]
[SUBARU]
She's snoring?
I make it a point to avoid
situations I can't control.
I don't deal well with people
doing things I don't expect.
But, it's only when those
unexpected things happen,
that you make little discoveries
and forge new friendships.
So, every once in a while,
and I mean every once
in a great while...
I guess surprises
might not be so bad.
♪
Maybe I'll give that...
a little more thought.
[snoring continues]
♪
-[NARUMI] Hey Haru!
-[footsteps running]
Where are you?
[HAYATO]
There you are!
[TWINS giggling]
[HARU]
Wha...
[screams]
What?
What in the world
is happening?
Are enemies attacking?
But this is supposed to be
a safe, quiet place!
-[HARU yelling fearfully]
-[HAYATO] Aw, she ran away!
[HARU] That's right!
Ms. Tora warned me about this.
[TORA] Just be sure you never
let your guard down.
‘Cause a fight
could sneak up on you
when you least expect it.
[HARU] Of course.
I can't just turn tail and run.
[hisses]
Bring it on, minions!
Hey, now,
you guys simmer down.
You can play with Haru,
but don't be too loud
or rough with her.
And don't chase her, either.
[BOTH]
Fine.
[HARU] Wait! It's that mildly
annoying human.
So, these smaller ones must be
his minions or something.
I definitely can't
let my guard down.
[giggles]
She's got a red bow, too!
[NAGISA] Yes, you're right.
Isn't her ribbon pretty?
-Come over here, Haru.
-Come here, Haru.
[HARU]
What should I do?
Now they've got me
surrounded! Huh?
That big one left.
Now it's just...
these weak-looking
"little ones."
They don't seem
so scary now.
[snickers]
My sheer courage must have
scared the big one off!
-[door thuds]
-[HARU] Huh?
-There she is!
-[HARU] It's him!
When did the super
annoying one get here?
Why do these humans
just keep coming?
Huh?
[yells]
It's all over!
One of them snuck up
behind me!
Guess I'll just have to...
[HARU grunts]
[ALL gasping]
[HARU inhales sharply]
[HARU]
Such a tiny human.
[TORA] That means you gotta look
after the runts, all right?
They won't last
long out here otherwise.
Whoa. Crazy.
For a second I was sure
Haru was about to scratch you.
But she's acting really calm.
[HARU] Attacking the weak
and defenseless isn't my style.
Haru is a very sweet kitty!
She doesn't seem bothered
at all by you holding her.
I wanna hold Haru, next!
-And then it's my turn!
-[KAWASE chuckles]
Maybe we should let her go
for a bit.
[HARU] They're definitely
invading my personal space,
but they're not
treating me like an enemy.
[HIROTO] Hey!
-[HARU] Huh?
[HARU]
I guess they're done now?
What was that all about?
Humans can be very confusing.
Oh, well, at least now
I can finally relax.
[doorbell ringing]
[WOMAN]
Delivery!
[HARU]
Huh?
Hold on. What's this?
[yelling]
I remember... that smell!
Thank you so much
for being patient.
-Hello! It's Haru!
-Hi, Narumi!
Haru, I didn't know
this was your friend's house!
[NARUMI]
No, we don't live here...
[HARU] That's the smell
of the super yummy food
I used to eat!
Huh?
[HARU] That yummy aroma
is making my mouth water!
[GIRL] Hey, Mom, look!
Didn't that kitty
used to come to our house?
[WOMAN] What?
Oh, my goodness,
it's the little cat
who loved my cooking so much!
So, she lives at this house?
Awesome!
[NARUMI] Haru, you mean
you know Haru the cat?
[HAYATO]
And you even have the same name!
Yeah. She used to
come by our house
and eat my mom's food!
But then one day
she just stopped showing up.
I'm so glad to know
she's okay!
How cool!
I've never met a cat
with my name before!
-Well. Time to go now.
-Oh. Okay.
[WOMAN]
Come on, Haru.
[HARU] What? Food? For me?
Can I eat it now?
I'm starving!
-Goodbye!
-[WOMAN chuckling]
See you later, Narumi!
[exclaims happily]
[HARU] I can't believe they
ordered my old favorite for me!
-Gimme! Now!
-[KAWASE] Everybody hidden?
[HARU]
Hey! What's going on?
Let me go.
I don't wanna stay back here.
[TWINS shushing]
A-poo-poo!
[HARU]
Hmm.
Heh. Well, that's
the saddest attempt
at a scary face
I've ever seen.
[MISORA giggles]
Okay, Haru!
You win!
[HARU] Huh?
What is she laughing about?
-What happened?
-[KAWASE] Guys, check it out!
Wanna see Haru play
with this toy?
[KIDS laughing]
[HARU]
Huh? What the... ?
I don't know what that is,
but I have to...
[yells]
How'd it get away?
[HARU grunting]
[exclaims]
[HARU]
What's happening?
My body!
It's moving against my will!
[ALL]
She's so cute!
[KIDS laughing]
[TARO]
So fun!
I wish I could play
with all of them!
[NARUMI] Yeah, next time we'll
bring our friends from class!
[SUBARU]
Ah... Uh-huh.
[TWINS]
Goodbye!
[door closing]
[HARU sighs]
[sighs]
Finally.
I was scared
they might never leave.
-[body falls]
-Huh?
He's as tired as I am.
Yeah, I guess he would be.
Come on.
You've got
to keep it together, human.
[SUBARU sighs heavily]
[HARU]
Just so we're clear,
I had it a lot tougher
than you did today.
Guess you had a pretty
rough day, too, didn't you?
[HARU]
Hmm.
Huh?
His smell is nice.
It makes me feel
safe and calm.
[MS. TORA] Just be sure
you never let your guard down.
[HARU]
I know that's right, Ms. Tora.
And I understand why.
But still...
Just for right now...
as long as I'm with him,
this is okay, right?
♪
What?
When did they do this?
[gasps]
"Where is the dictionary?"
Wait, did they hide it?
Why would they?
Where is it? Little jerks!
[HARU]
Hey, calm down!
The food is right here,
human, see?
[SUBARU]
Where is it?
[TARO] Today was such a fun,
exciting time, don't you think?
[HARU] What?
There was nothing fun about it!
[TARO]
You didn't have a good time?
[HARU] No, I got chased around
by those little minions all day!
[TARO]
Exactly!