-[rain pouring]
-[wind whistling]
No. You gotta be kidding.
[SUBARU] Yeah. Afraid so.
All the flights were canceled.
No. But I did catch a bullet
train at the last second.
[HIROTO] Sounds like a mess.
Know how far out you are?
I just got on, so I won’t be
back for another four hours.
In the meantime, can you stop by
and check on Haru?
[HIROTO] Sure thing.
Don’t stress out too much, okay?
Yeah, thank you.
[sighs]
[SUBARU]
It’s really pouring out there.
Aw, jeez,
it’s even worse back home.
I’ll be back soon, Haru.
Hang in there.
[rain pouring]
[HARU] It’s morning
and he still isn’t back?
What gives?
He's never been gone
this long before.
-[clattering]
-[HARU shrieks]
[HARU]
What was that?
-[wind whistling]
-[leaves rustling]
[HARU] Whoa,
that doesn’t look good at all!
-[rain pounding]
-[HARU whimpers]
[HACHI]
Help, Sis! Where are you?
[SIBLING]
I'm scared.
[BOTH whimpering]
Make it stop!
-[HARU] Hey!
-[KITTENS gasp]
[KITTENS]
Sis!
[HARU] I’ll keep you safe.
Be brave, okay?
[KITTENS]
Okay!
[HARU]
What if he's lost?
Or scared somewhere
and he can’t get back?
-[clattering]
-[HARU whimpers]
There he is!
-[lock turning]
-[door opens]
[HARU] I was really starting
to worry about you!
[grunting]
[grunting continues]
[HIROTO]
Crap! I can’t get it to shut!
[HARU]
It’s not him.
Then... where is he?
-[grunting]
-[door bangs]
[gasps]
♪
[HARU] He’s in trouble.
I have to go help him!
Huh? Was that... ?
Haru!
I screwed up.
[HARU] Hold on!
I promise I’ll save you!
-You let Haru outside?
-I’m really sorry!
I couldn’t shut the door because
of the wind and then she...
Hello?
Hey, you okay, man?
-Subaru, you there?
-Uh. yeah.
I was just thinking,
that’s all.
Don't you worry.
I'm gonna go out there
and look for her right now!
[SUBARU] No, hang on a second.
I have an idea.
It’s probably better
if you stay there at the house.
Someone should be home
in case Haru comes back.
[HIROTO]
Got it.
-[wind rushes]
-[SUBARU gasps]
-As for me...
-[tires screech]
[engine zooming]
[SUBARU]
What if she got in an accident?
No. Don’t even think about it.
I don’t want to go
through that again.
I can’t.
I won’t let it happen.
I have enough regrets!
[HARU]
Where could he have run off to?
[whimpers]
Not here.
Not here, either.
[gasps]
Pull it together!
I can’t be scared!
I have to protect him!
[SUBARU panting]
[SUBARU]
Come on, focus.
[gasping]
[panting]
No good.
Um, excuse me!
A quick question.
-Yeah?
-I’m looking for my cat.
Maybe you’ve seen her somewhere?
About this big?
And, let’s see,
she has black fur?
Well, she’s got white fur, too.
Just mostly black.
-Sorry. Haven’t seen a cat.
-I’ll keep looking.
But jeez, in this weather,
I probably wouldn’t even notice
if one ran straight past me.
[SUBARU gasps]
♪
[panting]
Where did you go?
Haru.
-[phone ringing]
-[gasps]
Hello?
[KAWASE]
Mikazuki! Where are you?
-Are you all right?
-Kawase. Hey.
Hiroto told me what’s going on.
I wanna help any way I can.
I’m on the way to your house
as we speak.
[SUBARU]
Huh?
[KAWASE] Hiroto probably knows
the area better than me,
so I’ll hold down the fort
and he can help you search.
[inhales sharply]
-Thank you so much.
-Try to stay calm.
Everything’s
gonna be all right.
We’ll find her!
-Okay.
-[KAWASE] Let’s be strategic.
Where do you think a cat might
go in this kind of weather?
If you put yourself
in Haru’s place, then may--
-[phone beeps]
-[SUBARU gasps]
[SUBARU]
The battery died.
[KAWASE] Where do you think
a cat might go
in this kind of weather?
[gasps]
[roll-up door clattering]
[NANA grunting]
[sighs]
-[SUBARU] Nana!
-[SUBARU panting]
[NANA] Subaru! Are you okay?
You’re soaking wet!
-What in the world is going-- ?
-It’s Haru.
[NANA gasps]
[SUBARU]
I can’t find her.
What? She ran away?
I can help you.
Wait here just a second.
Let me grab a few things.
[NANA]
Haru used to be a stray, right?
So she probably knows
her way around here.
Normally a cat would be hiding
under something near its home,
but if she’s not there,
she might have wandered
further than you’d think.
[gasps]
♪
[NANA] I know the weather
isn’t exactly ideal for this.
But if you leave her food out
in front of your house,
she might follow the scent
and come home.
♪
[NANA] Also, cats have
their own territory.
She might go someplace familiar,
or someplace she’s been fed.
[panting]
[SUBARU]
Wait. Maybe...
Haru! Haru!
Haru!
-[wind rushing]
-[rain pouring]
Not here, either.
What now?
[HARU] Where are you?
You can come out now!
I’m here for you!
You don’t have to be afraid!
We can go home!
-[wind rushing]
-[HARU whimpers]
[cries out]
[SUBARU]
Haru! Haru!
[wind rushes]
[HARU]
That was a close one!
[grunting]
-[clamoring]
-[surprised meowing]
[frustrated grunt]
[HARU]
What is the deal here?
That’s pretty tall.
-[wind rushing]
-[HARU cries out]
It'll be fine.
Nothing I can’t handle!
-[wind rushes]
-[HARU whimpers]
[whimpering]
I’m not scared.
I’m just resting for a second.
-[splashing]
-[cries out]
[gasps]
[SUBARU]
Haru!
-[HARU whimpers]
-[HARU] Was that?
[SUBARU]
Haru!
[HARU]
I’m not hearing things!
That’s his voice.
-[SUBARU] Haru!
-[HARU] He’s calling for me!
[wailing meow]
Where are you?
[footsteps running]
♪
It’s you!
I can’t believe it.
I found you!
[laughing]
[yelling]
-[splashing]
-[SUBARU yells]
[sighs]
[gulps, sniffles]
You’re okay.
I’m so glad.
[SUBARU sobbing]
[SUBARU grunts]
-I’m stuck.
-[frustrated meowing]
Hey! Stop!
I can’t have you flipping out!
-[HIROTO] Subaru!
-[angry meowing]
It’s Haru!
I knew you could find her!
What’s, uh, going on
with your butt?
[SUBARU groans]
It’s stuck in the trench.
[BOTH gasp]
[HIROTO laughing]
Here, Subaru.
Reach out and give me your hand.
-I’ll pull you out of there.
-Okay. I’ll try.
Here. Take her.
[gasps]
♪
-Something wrong?
-Oh, sorry!
I was just thinking, you haven’t
changed a bit since we met!
♪
[KAWASE] Well, that was
wet and stressful,
but I’m so glad Haru’s safe!
The ramen you brought
back from Tokushima
should be ready
any second now!
Thanks a ton
for your help and everything.
[NANA]
Sorry for the wait!
-One clean Haru, nice and warm!
-[KAWASE] Her first bath?
This is a milestone moment
for Haru-kitty!
-[HARU hisses]
-[KAWASE laughs]
♪
[slurping]
-That’s good!
-I’m glad I did it justice!
♪
[eager munching]
-[HIROTO] See ya!
-[door closes]
We ended up staying
so late. Hope it wasn’t a pain.
Get some rest. I’m sure you’re
exhausted after your trip.
You and Haru
can both sleep in late!
-I’ll see you again!
-Yeah, maybe so.
-Thank you!
-[ALL] Huh?
You saved me and Haru.
I couldn’t have
pulled this off alone.
[HARU]
I feel like I need to be strong,
when I see him tear up.
But when I see him
smile like that,
I want to be even stronger.
I wonder why that is?
[wailing meow]
[HARU] There you are!
Wait! That wall is slippery!
If you try to come down here,
we’ll both be stuck!
[laughing]
-[SUBARU yells]
-[HARU screams]
-[splashing]
-[SUBARU yells]
[HARU] Jeez, you really are
a dummy, aren’t you?
[HARU]
Now what are we gonna do?
-[sniffles] You're okay.
-[HARU] Huh?
Why do you look sad?
Did you hurt yourself?
Wh-whoa! What is this about?
You’re okay. I’m so glad.
[HARU] I guess you were
pretty scared after all.
Well, nice job
hanging in there!
[SUBARU gasps]
♪
[HARU]
What the heck are you doing?
Why aren’t we going home?
Did you get hungry
and stop moving around again?
-Now’s not the time!
-[SUBARU sighs]
[HARU]
Come on! Come on! Hurry!
What happens if you
fall asleep down here?
We’re in this together,
you know!
You’re useless!
Let me go and I’ll find
a way out for us, okay?
-[HIROTO] Subaru!
-[HARU gasps]
[HARU]
What’s happening? Whoa, wait!
Don’t worry about me,
save him first!
He’s hungry!
[HARU]
Oh, good.
Even if he can’t move anymore,
that giant can carry him.
[HARU whimpering]
-What are you doing to me?
-[whimpering]
We’ll be done soon. Don’t worry.
Good girl!
[HARU whimpering]
[NANA] Sorry for the wait!
One clean Haru, nice and warm!
[HARU]
I’m exhausted.
[KAWASE]
Her first bath?
This is a milestone moment
for Haru-kitty!
[HARU]
This guy again?
He’s the last thing
I need right now!
[yelling]
-[exhausted sigh]
-I’m hungry.
-[HIROTO laughing]
-[SUBARU slurping]
[ALL laughing]
[HARU]
This is so yummy!
Good!
Nice to see you’re eating!
[eager munching]
[SUBARU]
She seems just fine.
[laughs softly]
It’s strange.
At some point, spending time
with other people
stopped being a chore.
-It’s different now.
-[gate closes]
But why? What changed in me?
-[SUBARU] Just us.
-[meowing]
[gasps]
[SUBARU]
It’s taken me a while.
But I finally realize
when this started.
The day I met you.
[HARU meowing]
[laughs softly]
Welcome home, Haru.
I never had to be alone.
[inaudible]
[SUBARU] There were always
connections out there,
waiting to be made.
It just takes a little courage
to bridge the distance.
That day,
when I reached out to you,
I didn’t know how big
my world would grow.
[birds chirping]
[chuckles]
How’s Mikazuki’s
new story coming? Anything yet?
[KAWASE]
Hmm.
He has a theme. It’s “family.”
[pen scratching]
[laughs]
[HARU] When you get yourself
into trouble,
I’ll come and rescue you.
[SUBARU] When you’re scared,
I’ll be brave and hold you.
[HARU] But if I can help it,
you’ll never be in trouble.
I’ll make sure your face looks
that happy all the time.
[SUBARU] But if I can help it,
you’ll never feel scared.
I’ll protect you.
Keep you safe and warm.
[HARU]
As long as we’re together...
[SUBARU]
There’s nothing to worry about.
-My roommate is a cat.
-[HARU] On his lap.
[SUBARU]
And sometimes...
-[HARU] On his head.
-[SUBARU] On my head.