[soft meowing]
[SUBARU]
I was awoken by my roommate.
[meowing continues]
She’s being
awfully noisy today.
I haven’t slept
properly in days.
Maybe I should go
into hibernation
after I make my deadline.
Well, I’ll just have to make do
with naps until then.
I got a text? Oh, crap!
This is from last night.
Oh, it’s just Hiroto.
[HIROTO] Sorry for barging in
on you the other day.
Anyway, you remember my sister
Narumi and her friend Haru?
Well, they want to come
visit Haru again.
They’ll be coming to play
with her tomorrow,
so you know the drill.
If that won’t work for you,
let me know!
[SUBARU]
Tomorrow?
-That's today!
-[doorbell rings]
[SUBARU gasps]
[ringing continues]
[SUBARU]
No! Why me?
[NARUMI]
Sorry, Subaru.
We didn’t know
you were sleeping.
Are you sure you don’t mind us
hanging out over here?
It’s fine.
You’re no trouble at all.
[SUBARU] I won’t accept pity
from a child!
[NARUMI] Oh, hey,
since you were so nice to us,
we brought you a present!
Ta-da! It’s a whole bunch
of food from Haru’s mom!
-Yummy!
-Hungry?
-[SUBARU] Huh?
-[stomach rumbles]
[NARUMI giggling]
I guess that’s a “yes,” huh?
[SUBARU] Thanks, but...
how’d you know I needed dinner?
My brother said. He told me
you always need more food!
-[SUBARU] Hiroto.
-[HIROTO chuckles]
[HARU meowing]
[GIRL laughs]
[GIRL]
Hi, Haru! Came to see us?
[SUBARU]
Haru! No!
I know! We should share some of
your mom’s food with Haru, too!
[GIRL]
Huh? No, it’ll make her sick.
They can eat some stuff,
but most people food
is too salty for cats,
especially if they eat
a whole bunch of it.
[NARUMI]
Aw, okay. Poor kitty.
[SUBARU]
I didn’t know that.
I guess I’ve never given Haru
anything but sashimi
and dry food, luckily.
[GIRL]
Um, Subaru,
is it time for Haru
to eat now, too?
Oh. Yeah, I guess.
Is it okay if I make the food
I used to make for her?
It’s easy to cook
and I brought all the stuff.
She used to like it so much.
I thought she might miss it.
[SUBARU]
Homemade cat food, huh?
If you don’t mind, then, sure.
[gasps in delight]
[chopping vegetables]
You chop up the veggies
real small, like this.
And once it starts to boil,
you turn down the heat.
Then just let it simmer till
it’s soft, and then you’re done!
[NARUMI]
Haru, you’re so cool!
[SUBARU]
She did that like a pro.
Hey, I can also make
some of this
into soup for you to eat.
Do you have another pot
I could use?
[SUBARU]
Uh, yeah. Let me find it.
[NARUMI]
Ooh, I’ll get the dishes ready!
-[NARUMI] Hey! Haru!
-[GIRL] Huh?
[NARUMI]
No kitties on the counter, okay?
It’s all right, Haru.
Calm down!
Uh, think fast!
[gasps]
[SUBARU groans]
[door rattling]
[clattering]
[angry meowing]
[long, angry meow]
-[GIRL] Dinner's ready!
-[NARUMI] Whoa, that looks good!
[GIRL]
Haru! Come and get it!
-Haru!
-[HARU meows]
[HARU munching]
[SUBARU]
Wow, she’s scarfing that down.
[GIRL]
Come on Subaru! Eat up!
[SUBARU]
Right.
[GIRL]
Time to dig in!
-[hands clap]
-Thanks, Haru, and Haru’s mom!
[SUBARU] Th--
Thank you for the food.
[slurping]
[NARUMI]
So good!
[SUBARU]
All my fatigue is melting away!
Oh, hey, Subaru,
why don’t you eat real food
like you’re supposed to?
[SUBARU coughing]
[NARUMI] My brother
gets worried about you.
Do you hate food or something?
Uh, no.
It’s nothing like that.
I try to eat, but sometimes,
when I’m here alone,
I forget.
Forget?
Don’t you get hungry?
[SUBARU]
Yeah, but...
I think I understand
how Subaru feels.
No way! You’re surrounded
by food every day!
How does that even work?
It’s not that I don’t
like my mom’s food.
It’s just, the restaurant
gets busy around dinner time.
So, I always end up
eating in a room alone
while my family’s
out there working.
I keep thinking,
“Oh, maybe I’ll eat later,”
but I never feel like it.
-[HARU meowing]
-Huh?
[GIRL] But all that changed
when Haru started coming by.
I had my mom teach me
how to make food for cats
so I could feed her
when she was at our house.
[gasps]
I still remember
the happy little face
she made the first time
I cooked for her.
I was so glad
that she liked it.
Ever since then,
I make sure I eat right
and enjoy my dinner,
just like her.
[SUBARU] Come to think of it,
I kind of do the same thing.
When Haru eats,
sometimes I will, too.
[NARUMI]
Look! She cleaned her plate!
[GIRL] Yay! I’m glad
she still likes my cooking!
Hey, Haru, are you gonna
take over the restaurant
-when you grow up?
-[GIRL] Hmm, I don't know.
My mom is such
a really good cook.
I don’t think
I could ever replace her.
[SUBARU]
Really?
‘Cause I think your food’s
pretty good already.
[GIRL giggling]
Hearing someone say that
makes me happier than anything.
[SUBARU'S MOM]
Hey, Subaru.
How do you like
the stew today?
I was afraid I made it
a little too spicy.
[SUBARU]
Huh?
♪
[SUBARU]
Tastes good, as usual.
It’s fine. Not too spicy.
Well, that’s good to hear.
[SUBARU]
Why did I say it like that?
I should have told her
how much I loved her cooking.
H-Hey.
Are you still hungry?
Want seconds?
You got a special treat
and you’re still not satisfied?
[exclaims] Look, she’s sleeping
on your lap!
Aw, I get sleepy when I have
a belly full of good food, too!
[SUBARU]
Haru. I am not your bed.
That was fun!
Thank you for letting us
come over today!
See you soon!
Oh, um, you think I could make
that food for Haru, too?
-[BOTH giggling]
-[GIRL] Yeah, of course!
We’ll make a super cute recipe
and bring it here for you!
-[SUBARU] Cute?
-[BOTH giggling]
Um, thanks.
But a normal recipe’s fine.
-[dishes clattering]
-[sighs]
[SUBARU]
Finally. Done.
It’s been a long time since
I had to wash so many dishes.
Maybe I should have dinner
with people more often.
-[birds chirping]
-[HARU meowing]
[meowing continues]
[SUBARU]
Noisy again, huh?
Give your roommate a break!
[munching]
[SUBARU] You like
your breakfast, don’t you?
What the heck?
[groans]
In crayon?
They must have dropped it off
before school.
[HARU meowing]
[SUBARU]
I guess I could make it.
I just need the ingredients.
I’ve never gone shopping
at a giant grocery store
like this before.
-Okay, let’s see...
-[DAUGHTER exclaims]
Your little book is cute!
[MOM] Sweetie, no! You leave
that awkward man alone!
[SUBARU]
Good start. Now for the carrots.
The vegetables over here
are all-you-can-carry!
Only 500 yen!
Supplies are limited!
[rumbling]
[clamoring]
[SUBARU] Stop it!
They’re just vegetables!
You’re crushing me!
[CUSTOMERS clamoring]
[SUBARU groans]
[SUBARU]
Now the meat.
[SUBARU groans]
There's a million
different kinds of chicken here.
Why is this a thing?
Calm down.
Check the recipe.
[groans]
I’ll just buy whatever.
I can ask 'em later.
I’m ready to get out of here.
[GROCER]
Hello, there!
Interested in our
meat selection, sir?
Would you like to try these?
They’re tasty!
[SUBARU]
No. I...
[GROCER 2]
Our seafood is on sale today!
[GROCER 3] These are going fast!
Better grab one!
[DAUGHTER]
Hey, it's that guy!
Show me your picture book!
Please?
-[GROCERS clamoring]
-[SUBARU] No, I-- I just...
[SUBARU sighs]
[SUBARU]
I’m weak. I couldn’t say no.
I need to check out
before I end up
buying a lifetime supply
of bananas or something.
-[HIROTO] Huh? Subaru?
-[SUBARU gasps]
No way.
Are you cooking?
For your cat?
This kind of looks
like overkill to me.
It is. I got roped in.
[phone dialing]
Hey. Narumi?
What kind of chicken
do you use
in that cat recipe
you gave to Subaru?
Cool. Just breast.
Got it.
[HIROTO] I know you’re
just doing your job,
but this guy lives alone.
There’s no way
he can eat all this stuff.
Sorry! I’ll come buy
some next time, okay?
[SUBARU gasps]
Hiroto.
[shopping bag rustling]
[SUBARU sighs]
That seriously wore me out.
[HIROTO] Thanks for the snack!
Good luck cooking!
[SUBARU]
I got lucky.
Sometimes, I don’t know
what I’d do without him.
Now, time to get serious
about cat food.
[chopping]
Okay.
Next, I just need to peel it.
Keep peeling.
Keep... peeling...
Did I mess up? That doesn’t even
look like a radish anymore.
No, I followed
the instructions.
It’s fine.
Just move onto the next step.
"Pieces that she can eat?"
-[SUBARU grunts]
-[HARU growls]
Stay still. I gotta measure
your mouth real quick.
-[angry meow]
-[SUBARU grunts]
[SUBARU] I don’t know how
I thought that was going to go.
Still, if I make
the pieces too big,
then they’ll get stuck
in her throat!
[SUBARU gasps]
Her dry food pieces
are seven millimeters across.
If I can keep it
under that, I’m good.
[sighs] Well, that was a trial.
Next is...
[grunts]
That’s a lot.
Still have to boil it, too?
Maybe I’ll call it
quits for today.
No. If a kid can do it,
I can do it.
For Haru.
-[strained grunt]
-[knife clanking]
[SUBARU groans]
[SUBARU] I’m being punished
for my pride, aren’t I?
[HARU meowing]
[SUBARU] Hey! No!
Are you hungry already?
[meowing]
[SUBARU] Sorry, this’ll take
a little while longer.
I really should just give her
the dry food, after all.
No, don’t give up yet!
It’ll be worth the wait!
I mean, I hope.
[meows]
[oven clicking]
Well, I made it
this far, somehow.
Now I can just relax
till it softens up.
Actually, I should throw
some together for myself, too.
It’s finally done!
Well, I think, at least.
Better poke it
to make sure it’s soft.
Haru.
[SUBARU]
I see. I should’ve known.
It’s no good when I make it.
I’ll eat alone.
[munching]
♪
She’s eating!
I’m not much
for helping others.
I don’t like changing my life
to accommodate someone else’s.
Most of the time, it’s more
trouble than its worth.
But this?
[laughs softly]
So good.
Again? You’re funny.
[SUBARU]
Having dinner together, huh?
I might have to make
a habit of this.
[HARU]
It’s that time again...
when he forgets to eat
and stops moving.
Jeez! Pull it together,
will you, human?
Get up and eat something!
[frustrated groan]
There! Took you long enough!
[doorbell rings]
[HARU]
Huh?
Wait! What’s going on?
What’s that noise? Is it bad?
Well, I did my job.
Whatever it is,
it’s your problem.
-[sniffs]
-[gasps]
I smell food!
I smell super yummy food!
[GIRL laughs]
Hi, Haru!
Came to see us?
[SUBARU]
Haru! No!
[HARU]
Gimme food!
Food! Food! Huh?
Wait, no.
He’s the one who needs
to eat right now, not me.
♪
[HARU]
Where is that smell coming from?
There must be something
yummy up here.
[NARUMI]
Hey! Haru!
No kitties on the counter,
okay?
[HARU groans] It’s that minion
from the other day!
If you think you can
take me one-on-one,
you’ve got
another thing coming!
[HARU]
Come to assist me, huh?
Good! Let’s trounce
that minion!
[hisses]
[heavy footstep]
Open up, you filthy traitor!
How dare you
treat me like this!
Huh? Changed your mind, then?
Maybe you’re not
so hopeless after all.
Just let me out and we’ll
settle this in no time!
[HARU grunts]
Fine!
Don’t come crying to me
when this blows up your face!
You’re dead to me!
Ah!
You don’t know
the first thing about gratitude!
I’ve been so worried about you
and this is the thanks I get?
[GIRL] Haru,
come and get it! Haru!
[HARU] I know that smell!
It’s the best food in the world!
-This is a dream come true!
-[munching]
It's so good!
Wait, I need to share
some of this food with him!
He’s the hungry one,
after all!
[gasps]
Oops. It was too yummy.
I ate it all.
But he looks like
he’s about to fall over.
That’s no good. I’m sorry.
I knew you were hungry, too!
But I couldn’t help it!
-[SUBARU] H-Hey.
-[HARU gasps]
[HARU]
You’ve got plenty of food!
[exhausted moaning]
-I was worried over nothing!
-[HARU'S GHOST giggling]
[HARU] But the next day,
it was the same old thing.
Hey! You still haven’t
eaten yet, have you?
Get it together, you dummy!
At this rate, you’re gonna
stop moving like before!
[screams]
Aw, I did it again!
I was supposed to save him some!
Great. Now what?
Hey, you’re gonna eat
something, aren’t you?
You didn’t give all
the food to me, right?
Huh? Where are you going?
Hey, come back here!
He’s acting all weird.
What’s going on?
He left all of a sudden,
came back all wobbly
and now he’s rooting
around in there.
Maybe he’s looking for food!
He tried to go hunting,
but he couldn’t find anything!
Oh, right. I ate all the food
in the food place. Shoot.
I better start
looking somewhere else.
Okay, whoa, this is new!
Sorry, there’s no food
in my mouth!
-It’s all my stomach now!
-Stay still!
I gotta measure
your mouth real quick.
[HARU fussing]
I know you’re hungry,
but you’re just gonna
have to trust me on this one!
How rude!
You must be really desperate!
But don’t worry, I’ve got this!
Miss Tora trained me,
after all.
I’m an expert hunter!
You’re mine now!
-[HARU grunting]
-[SUBARU] Hey! No!
[HARU]
See? I found food for you!
Now grab some and eat,
why don’t you?
Are you hungry already?
[HARU]
There you go. Almost there.
[screams]
No!
[HARU]
Why won’t you eat?
[frustrated groan]
-This is exhausting.
-[stomach growls]
Great, and now I’m hungry too.
But this time, I gotta
take care of him, first!
Wait! That smell.
Were you eating something
awesome in secret without me?
[SUBARU]
Haru.
[HARU screams]
[HARU]
I get to eat the best food...
Again! No! Resist!
He needs to eat first!
Hey, did you find enough food
for yourself, too?
I’ll eat alone.
[HARU sighs]
[HARU] Good. You finally
got something yummy!
Now I can eat without having
to worry about you for once!
[eager munching]
I feel like I’m in heaven!
[cries joyfully]
Ah! Every time with this food.
[SUBARU laughs softly]
So good.
[HARU] What was that?
Is he happy?
I don’t think I’ve heard him
make that noise before.
[HARU]
Honestly!
You have no idea how much
stress you put me through!
But as long as you’re eating
and staying strong enough
for another day,
then I can relax.
That’s all I need.
[HARU] Have you heard of
“eating in moderation?”
[TARO]
Nope. What’s that?
[HARU] It’s the name
of something really bad!
[TARO]
Oh? You mean it’s scary?
[HARU] Eating in moderation
is terrifying!