[NARRATOR]
For untold centuries,
there have been powerful
warriors who fought against
the various crises that
threatened our world.
They harnessed
the power of the monsters
and forged a bond which
eased the planet's anger.
They were the Dragon Callers.
[NARRATOR] Dragon Callers
are born with the special power
to bridge the gap between
the realms of nature.
Mankind and monsters.
When fear and hatred contaminate
the elements that surround us...
...the Dragon Callers will
rise up with their monsters
and restore balance
to our world.
The deep blue sea.
It reflects the distant
blue of the sky above.
The sun is warm. It's as
if the longer I stay here,
The more likely my wounded
heart might find love.
Not paying attention
hurts sometimes!
Be more careful, tama!
You're the one who
should be more careful!
Relax! Why don't you come
play volleyball with us?
You're young. If I played you,
it wouldn't be fair!
Hey, why don't you ask Charo?
[gasps]
[shouts]
Don't do it, buddy!
[CHARO yelps]
Things can't be that grim, man!
I can't even count the number
of times I've been shot down
in the game of love.
But this weather has brought
the hopeless romantic in me
back to life!
And though I face
constant rejection,
I have to hold on to hope!
Even though she'll probably
turn me down again!
You know, I'm starting to
feel really sorry for you.
Of course. I'm a total mess!
But if I can go
on living, so can you!
He's using his pain to connect!
Tama, tama!
Yeah, okay. I'm not really
sure where that came from,
but thanks for sharing.
But you were staring into the
sea all depressed-looking!
You had the face of a jumper.
I couldn't just stand by!
I may have been feeling
a little depressed,
but I wasn't about
to jump, you dingbat!
I get it. You're worried
about your hometown.
[CHARO]
Mm-hm
[GARNET] The Ancient of
Wood isn't doing well
and Libria's in some
serious trouble!
What did she mean by
"serious trouble"?
Maybe it could
be that. Or worse!
What if this was what
she was talking about?
[ACE]
Charo, snap out of it, dude!
[TAMAZO]
Come back to us, tama!
The air here is
ultra-fresh, tama!
It doesn't look like the place
is in serious trouble to me.
He's right.
Yeah, I know.
[VILLAGERS chatter]
[TAMAZO]
Tama?
[ALL grunt]
[VILLAGERS shouting]
What's got them so upset?
They're rooting for
different candidates
to replace the Ancient.
[gasps]
Wait, to replace him?
What's wrong with
Master Tinbell?
The doctors say
he's doing better now.
But when he first fell ill,
it didn't look good.
So Master Tinbell
announced that he would
step down as the
Ancient of Wood.
He's named two of his most
capable students as the
finest potential candidates
to serve as his replacement.
[LADIES cheer]
And, speak of the devil,
here comes one now.
That fellow in the green
outfit is named Klein.
[KLEIN] When I become
the new Ancient of Wood,
I swear to put the people's
needs before my own, and usher
in a new era of prosperity
for the city of Libria!
[LADIES cheer]
[KLEIN chuckles]
Ugh, What a pompous
know-it-all. Who is he?
He's one of Master
Tinbell's top students!
He's also one of the strongest
Dragon Callers around!
The general consensus is that
he's the one most likely
to be named as the
Ancient's successor.
So who'd the Ancient pick as
an alternative to this guy?
Well, the rumors around
town say he's a human
Dragon Caller who is every
bit as good as Klein!
But I can't personally
vouch for that,
since I've never seen
this Torlie in action.
Mister Torlie?
I take it you know this guy?
[gasps] I got to know him
after he saved my life.
[FRIEND A gasps]
Wow, how pretty!
[CHARO]
Huh? What?
[FRIEND A] Duh! The Drops,
of course! Just look!
Uh...
Can't you see 'em, Charo?
Uh. Yeah, sure I can!
Wow! So pretty!
[CHARO] At first, I just
lied and pretended
that I could see the Drops too.
I was afraid of being
the odd one out.
But it wasn't long before
they learned the truth.
[BOYS laugh]
[grunts]
Beat it, loser!
You can't even see the Drops,
so you'd only slow us down!
[gasps]
[roars]
[whistle blows]
[TORLIE grunts]
[TORLIE]
I'll take care of this.
[CHARO] He protected
me from the monster.
Even though it put
his own safety at risk.
He must've been frightened too.
But he held his ground.
Watching Mister Torlie fend off
the monster made me dream about
someday becoming a
Dragon Caller like him.
But when I talked
about my dream,
everybody just laughed at me.
They said that if I
couldn't even see Drops,
I didn't stand a chance. That no
amount of research or practice
would make me a Dragon Caller.
[TORLIE] I'm sure you'll be
able to see Drops one day!
As long as you don't give up,
you always have a chance!
But you have to
believe in yourself!
If you just keep on trying,
then I know your
dream will come true!
Do you really mean it?
And that's why Torlie's
a hero of mine.
My hope is to be just
like him when I grow up.
Heh! Sorry I went
on there for a minute.
I have a bad habit of
dreaming too big sometimes.
Charo.
Why don't I take you guys to
the library? I'd like for you to
get the chance to
meet Mister Torlie too!
Library? Isn't he
a Dragon Caller?
He is! And he's also
an archaeologist,
studying Dragoza Island!
But he mostly stays holed up
in the library doing research.
Well you should tell Torlie that
fresh air is important, too,
so he needs to get out more.
Whoa, hey! Stop it!
That isn't food, little guy!
Still yummy!
I want seconds, tama!
What is wrong with him?!
[ACE chuckles]
[CHARO laughs]
Nothing's changed!
[ENJU squeaks]
[CHARO]
Hey, Enju!
[laughs]
Stop it, that tickles!
Your forehead's
healing up nicely!
[ENJU squeaks]
Mister Torlie?
[crashing]
Ow, ow...
[CHARO]
Mr. Torlie!
Oh, Charo? Why are you he--
[CHARO shouts]
Um. Are you all right?
[TORLIE grunts]
Yes, I'll be fine.
Ow, ow, ow.
This is one of the guys
the Ancient picked?
For real?
"Ow, ow, ow" tama!
[chuckles]
I have to admit,
I'm glad to see being a
bigshot hasn't changed you!
A bunch of the townspeople
are making this out to be
a big deal, but I'm still
just the same old me.
I was pretty surprised
to hear that you were
one of the Ancient's
chosen candidates.
But the way you're willing to
put yourself out in front of
other people! I think you'll
make the perfect Ancient,
and bring harmony
between man and monster!
I still don't know if
I'm fit to be an Ancient.
But some of the townspeople
seem to think I am,
or else they wouldn't
be supporting me.
Oh, yeah! Guess what?
They're still coming in
more faintly than I'd like,
but guess who can
sometimes see Drops?
Hey! That's great news, Charo!
Everything has worked out
exactly like you said it would!
You told me not to give up,
because one day my dreams
would finally come true!
You gave me hope.
I've cherished those words.
[gasps]
[ACE gasps]
[TAMAZO]
Tama?
--[ACE, TIGER pant]
--[TAMAZO] Tama?
[FAFNIR roars]
Yo! Y'Need a hand?
No need, I'm finished.
Whoa.
Unfortunately, the Ancient's
power is waning, and so is
the strength of the magic seal
that keeps the monster away
from our town.
What?
[TINBELL]
But never you worry.
The new Ancient
may not seem like it,
but he's reliable in
times of crisis.
The lad just needs a fire lit
under him from time to time.
[ACE]
What was that about?
[TIGER]
Not sure.
[TAMAZO]
Tama?
[gasps]
[CROWD mutters]
[ACE gasps]
What's with the commotion?
'Scuse me? What's going on?
Master Tinbell's
making an announcement.
Yeah, but about what?
[CHARO gasps]
Hey, it's that old man again!
So, when did you
meet Master Tinbell?
Master Tinbell? Say what?!
You mean that old dude's
the Ancient of Wood?
We shall hold a
battle to determine
which of these contenders
will be the next Ancient.
[CROWD cheers]
The candidate
who claims victory
over the other will be
named my successor.
[chuckles]
[grunts]
[gasps]
[WOMAN A]
Klein's going to win for sure!
[WOMAN B] The battle's
a waste of time, really.
That's not true. I think
Torlie has the potential
to be a great human
Dragon Caller.
It will be an honor to test
my prowess against his.
I only hope that this
fight won't end for you
like your exam.
[grunts]
[KLEIN] Although, you've become
much stronger since then,
haven't you? So I'm sure
you'll do just fine.
Get a good night's rest. I want
an actual challenge out there.
I'm sure that you
can beat him, Torlie!
As long as you give
it your very best!
[exhales] You're right.
If I work hard,
there's no stopping me!
[CHARO]
That's the attitude!
Twelve! Thirteen!
[MAN A cheers]
[CROWD chatters]
I saved some seats for
you kids down front!
Thank you, sir!
So thoughtful, tama!
[CROWD cheer]
[KLEIN chuckles]
[TIGER]
Ha! He's still a pompous snob!
Hmph.
Wow. You changed your hair.
That 'do doesn't work for you.
The more I look, the more
annoyed it makes me!
Oh, man! It took me two hours
to get it like this!
You don't even
have hair, Tamazo!
Hey there! How's the
Wood City treating you boys?
[ACE]
Garnet!
I really wanted to
come with you guys,
but I had important
business to attend to.
Since when is going to
the spa "business"?
[GARNET] I'm spending
some quality time
with my new bestie,
Master Eldora!
And y'know, Libria just
seems sort of lame.
I doubt I'd meet
anyone interesting.
[ACE grunts]
[GARNET gasps]
Who's the stud-muffin?
Huh? He's a candidate for
the new Ancient of Wood.
He is totally my type!
And with a promising future
as a potential Ancient!
Hold on! I'm on my way!
[ELDORA] Garnet? Where
do you think you're going?
Seriously?
[GARNET] This is fun.
We should do it again!
[CHARO] You've spent years
training for a moment
like this to come along.
You're gonna do great!
[squeaks]
Yeah...
[CROWD cheers]
Okay, Torlie! Just relax!
Take a breath, and relax.
He's so tightly wound,
it's making me nervous.
I hope he doesn't throw up.
Yeah. Me too!
[CROWD cheers]
[grunts] You will only have
one shot at this battle.
And your very pride as a Dragon
Caller will be on the line!
[gasps]
Don't go losing your
focus now, Torlie.
Surely you don't want to repeat
the mistake you made back then.
[TORLIE grunts]
[grunts]
[KLEIN]
Just try to relax, Torlie.
I'm certain you can tap
into your true strength.
[TORLIE grunts]
Oh, my! I think those
robes they're wearing
are advanced
wood-element Soul Armor.
Those are actual Soul Armors?
I like 'em! What other
colors do they come in?
But why are they both
wearing the same armor?
In order to keep their
leader skills the same.
Now let the battle begin!
[CROWD cheers]
Release!
Now, Release!
[MONSTERS growl]
[GIGA WOODSIE growls]
[KLEIN]
I've got you now!
It's half-time! Stand down!
It's gonna be fine! If anyone
can catch up, it's you!
[TORLIE grunts]
I bet you've got a killer
move or two up your sleeve
that'd really turn
this fight around!
Charo, I don't
think I can do it.
Huh?
This was impossible
from the very start!
There's no way I have what it
takes to be the next Ancient!
You're not giving up, are you?
[TORLIE sighs]
Have you forgotten what
you told me, Torlie?
"As long as you don't give up,
there's always a chance."
[TORLIE exhales]
[TORLIE]
Charo!
[CHARO sobs]
As long as you don't give up,
you'll always have a chance!
But you have to
believe in yourself.
If you just keep on trying,
then I know your
dream will come true!
[sobs]
Whoa! Is that?
[FAFNIR roars]
It's him again!
It looks creepy, tama!
This is bad.
Unfortunately, the Ancient's
power is waning,
and so is the strength
of the magic seal
that keeps the monster
away from our town.
We've gotta try to stop it-
[gasps]
[ACE]
Charo! Hold on!
[TINBELL]
So the seal finally broke.
Second half begin!
[shouts]
[gasps]
[KLEIN] Well this is easy.
Looks like I'm the new Ancient.
Charo! Would you
just wait a sec?
[CHARO]
I guess you can't dream big
if you want to have a chance.
I was wrong about everything.
Charo.
Even if you don't want
to give up on your dream,
there comes a time when you
have to face the facts.
[BOTH shout]
[roars]
[ACE, CHARO shout]
[CROWD screams]
[TORLIE gasps]
[ACE]
I won't let you through!
Tama!
Uh, Seriously?
[roars]
[ALL grunt]
So listen, Torlie.
I'm going to make sure everyone
has evacuated safely.
I'll leave him to you!
[TORLIE gasps]
Right this way, everyone!
That jerk ran away!
[TAMAZO] Looks like
pretty-boy's a chicken!
[TORLIE gasps]
[TINBELL]
I'll handle this.
[ALL gasp]
[CHARO]
Master Tinbell!
[roars]
Charo!
No! If you're looking
to fight, I'm right here!
[CHARO]
Torlie!
[yells]
Torlie...
[GIGA WOODSIE growls]
[grunts]
There are no more
Wood Drops to pull!
[FAFNIR roars]
[TORLIE grunts]
[gasps]
[TORLIE]
I can use the water underground.
[TORLIE] Fortoytops, shift!
Guard Stance: Wood!
[growling]
[TORLIE] Highlander!
Attack Stance: Wood!
[HIGHLANDER growls]
He did it!
Wow, that was awesome!
He's the bravest dude
I've ever seen!
Kick its tail, tama!
[MAN B]
We believe in you!
[WOMAN C]
Please win!
[TORLIE]
Giga Woodsie! Woodsie Attack!
[GIGA WOODSIE growls]
[shouts]
[TORLIE] Giga Woodsies have the
ability to triple the attack
power of all balance
types for a short time.
[CHARO]
Mister Torlie!
You did it! Do you realize
you saved the entire city?
I always knew you
were a real hero!
[gasps]
[CHILD A]
Torlie!
[CROWD cheers]
I'm glad you didn't give up!
All you needed was a
little push to shine!
Master Tinbell.
[TINBELL] You have a
kind heart, my boy,
and you always put
others before yourself.
And that's what makes you
worthy of being an Ancient.
One who understands the
needs of Dragonoids, humans,
and monsters.
You are the next
generation of Ancient.
Torlie, I'm proud of you!
Thank you, sir.
[TINBELL] Remember that
the kindness in your heart
is your greatest strength.
Polish your pure heart,
that it may shed its light
on the path
towards a better life.
I will.
[TINBELL] May the future of
Libria be full of happiness!
And may you all be blessed!
[MAN C] Long live the new
Ancient of Wood, Torlie!
[WOMAN D]
Bless you, Master Torlie!
I've decided that I'm never
ever going to give up
on my dreams again!
As long as I don't give up,
there's still a chance.
Someday, I'll be just
like you, Master Torlie!
[TORLIE chuckles]
Chase that dream!
[CHARO]
I'm home!
Charo!
Welcome home, honey!
[CHARO]
I brought my friends with me.
[TIGER, ACE]
Pleased to meet you!
[TAMAZO]
Hello, tama!
Nice to meet you!
And thank you so much for
keeping an eye on our son!
[TAMAZO]
No problem at all, sir.
I try to take good
care of these guys.
[ACE] Oh yeah, we'd all be
really lost without you!
Yeah right!
[CHARO] Mr. Torlie
seems down in the dumps,
even though he was picked to
be the new Ancient of Wood.
And it seems like something's
disrupting the forest, as well.
[CHARO]
Next time! "The New Ancient".
I just wish I could
be more helpful.