Target moving out from B-3!
AFS Tank 2.
It's moving towards you.
Can you see it?
It's closing in!
Where? I don't see--
[grunts]
[TANK COMMANDER A]
Astro-Particle Cannon! Fire!
We knocked it down, sir!
Good! Turn on the Anti-Rave!
Devi?
We've found it.
Right where Master Jest
said it would be, Devi!
Go. Follow it.
[roars]
[RADIO DJ]
Good morning, listeners!
Another beautiful
sunny day in Vienna City!
And it looks like it's
gonna stay that way,
so get out there
and catch some rays!
But if you're
all out of SPF 50,
there's a mega event scheduled
at the Dragon Museum--
Are you sitting down? Because--
[LANCE] Devi,
could you turn that thing off?
[DEVI]
Devi...
I'll need you to pick us up,
but until then,
go enjoy the mountains.
[roars softly]
[SIDONIA sighs]
How lovely!
Hmm? Ace, dear!
Good morning!
Mrs. Sidonia!
Good morning to you, too!
[SIDONIA]
Hold on!
You're heading to the
market, aren't you?
Not taking your normal shortcut?
What, you think
I didn't notice?
[laughs]
[SIDONIA]
Grandpa? Ace is coming.
Let him through, would you?
Good morning!
[GRANDPA]
Go ahead and hop over!
Okay.
And if you see any top-notch
fish, pick one up for me.
[ACE]
You got it!
Looks good.
I'm ready for checkout.
May I please buy them?
All of our eggs are fresh,
laid by our own chickens
every morning.
I know.
But most folks don't know that
the health of the individual
hens varies from day to day.
Of course!
But you can tell.
Uh. Can tell what?
You pick the best--
and it goes well past
choosing between eggs.
Walt from the fish shop
says you always
have an eye for
the freshest squid, too.
Such discerning taste, my boy,
I'd be proud to call you
my adopted son!
Stop shoveling your nonsense!
He already has Lena
to look after him.
If she wants to move in,
that's fine! Ha!
So Ace, you think
that she'd be interested?
[WIFE growls]
You conniving little--!
--Thanks, guys! See ya later!
--[SHOP MASTER grunting]
--Just a joke!
--[KOMIYA] Oh, yeah!
You got him good!
Now work the body! Tire him out!
[yelling, laughing]
[ACE]
I can't really explain why.
Some of 'em just sparkle.
And they always end up
being the best.
[WIFE] The real joke
is how weak you are!
[SHOP MASTER]
I-I'm sorry, honey! Aah!
We've searched Area D,
but there's no sign of it.
Are you sure we're in
the right place?
This is definitely
the region where it fell.
It can't have just disappeared!
[DIVER B]
What's that?!
Huh...?
[SAILOR A]
Something off starboard!
A Sea Dragon?
Plesios.
[SAILOR B]
Mark BP confirmed!
But why would a Type-R be here?
It looks like he wasn't
able to find it, Devi.
It's all right.
If you couldn't find it down on
the sea floor, then no one can.
Time to go back, now.
Are you sure that thing
even landed here?
Yes, I'm absolutely
certain of it.
Which means...
it didn't stay long.
And I don't see
any tracks, Devi.
[LANCE]
There's no sign of it at all.
Let me guess--We're gonna
comb this entire island
to find it, aren't we?
This here's one fine specimen!
[SIDONIA] Tell Lena
I'll be swinging by later!
'Kay, see ya!
[VOICE]
Ace!
Was that you guys?
Did you hear that sound?
[ACE]
Dragoza Island...
[meows]
Poor kitty!
She's too scared to climb down.
[HIYORI]
Just jump, kitty.
[RYOTARO]
You'll be all right!
[meows]
I'll meetcha halfway!
[HIYORI gasps]
Thank you!
[RYOTARO]
Wow, good job!
Be more careful!
Oh, wait. That collar...
[HARU] Someone must've kidnapped
her... What am I gonna do...?
[LENA] You shouldn't
jump to conclusions.
She's probably just fine. We'll
go look for her, I promise.
Just wait for Ace to come home.
[HARU]
Happy...
--[door clacks]
--[ACE] I'm back.
[LENA]
Oh, hi, Ace.
[gasps] What?
Well, I never... [giggles]
Oh, Mrs. Sidonia told me she
was gonna come by here later.
[LENA giggles]
'Kay!
Hey, Haru. What's wrong?
Have you got a tummy ache?
[HARU gasps]
Who'd come grab a coffee
if their stomach was hurting?!
[gasps]
Happy!
Jeez, where'd you run off
to? I was worried!
I saw her collar and knew right
away it had to be your cat.
You mean you kidnapped Happy
so you could
hold her for ransom!
Excuse me?
I was just joking!
Thank you, Ace!
Take whatever you want as
a token of my gratitude.
--[ACE] This is my house!
--[LENA giggles]
[ACE] Get serious.
You, a Dragon Caller?
How insulting!
What's with the tone?
[ACE] Sorry, but you
can't even see Drops.
[HARU]
Maybe for now.
But it may be something
I just kinda grow into.
Thanks a bunch for
coming in today!
You guys have the tastiest
sunny-side up eggs in town!
I'll come back tomorrow.
[LENA]
Thank you! See you then!
[door opens, bells jingle]
[HARU] You should be
a Dragon Caller, too!
Unless you're chicken!
Who, me? Never really
thought about it.
[HARU]
Girls will adore you.
Really?
[LENA growls]
Yeah, of course!
Callers are strong.
Gee, Haru, I wonder
what you're insinuating.
[chuckles]
Yeah, I wonder.
Hey, let's move on!
Didja hear about the meteor
that fell into Vienna Bay
this morning?
[ACE]
Huh...?
[COMMANDER YAMAKI]
It's still missing?
Yes.
We've doubled the search area,
but haven't found anything.
We'll keep looking.
We're positive we have
the right location?
[NUDO] It was on our radar
until it fell to 16 feet
above sea level.
That was when the
observation post in Cape Horai
reported spotting a uniquely
massive water column.
[COMMANDER YAMAKI] So what
does this information tell us?
That this particular meteor
was anything but ordinary.
Shall we notify the mayor?
He wouldn't know what to do
with the information if we did.
I've already reported
the abnormal Drop readings
to the man, but he
didn't seem to care.
Once the people have
actually seen the danger,
they'll learn to fear.
[sighs] And judging by the
energy response on our sensors,
they won't have
to wait for long.
[NUDO] The Sci-Techs
are making solid progress.
They're certainly
earning their funding.
We should be able to show it
on screen in the near future.
Make it our top priority.
[phone rings]
[COMMANDER YAMAKI]
What's wrong?
It's the final report from
the captain of the patrol boat.
According to him,
a Dragon Caller,
along with his sea-dragon-type
monster were seen searching
for the meteor's landing site.
[HARU] But it may be something
I just kinda grow into.
[ACE] I've been seeing more
and more of them recently.
[VOICE]
Ace!
[gasps]
Here! For helping me.
Thank you.
Hey... Has Happy ever,
like, spoken to you?
[HARU]
Hmm... Huh.
[ACE]
What's up?
Well, the good news is at
least you don't have a fever.
[ACE] Yeah, I could've
told you that!
Tell me, how long has the
patient been hearing voices?
Do they tell you to burn things?
Ugh. Just forget it.
No way!
Uh, yes way.
[HARU] This is so exciting!
I can't believe it!
Happy, come with me!
Hold these, Ace!
[grunting]
Whaddaya think you're doing?!
[HARU]
Excuse me!
You're Mr. Lance, aren't you?
You're so cool!
What brings you to Vienna City?
So that's Lance?
They call him the
Crown Prince of Ice!
That's awesome!
[ACE]
He's famous?
Is he a Dragon Caller?
And guess what? I'm trying
to be a Dragon Caller, too!
Like her?
This is my cat, Happy!
Do you think she has what it
takes to work with
a hotshot Dragon Caller
such as yourself?
This guy's exceedingly annoying!
Calm down!
You have the wrong guy.
Devi.
--[DEVI] Devi!
--[HARU gasps]
Wait... Mr. Lance...
He really is as cold as ice...
--So cool!
--[HAPPY screeches]
What's wrong, Master?
[LANCE]
Nothing.
[ACE]
That guy's just a show off.
[VOICE]
Ace!
[gasps]
Now that's an egg.
[LENA]
Thanks! See you soon!
[gasps]
Hey there!
Where have you been?
Haru is furious!
She said you abandoned her
on your little date-- [gasps]
Oh? Yeah, right.
But that wasn't a date.
[LENA]
And what have you got there?
U-Uh... [chuckles]
Oh, this? It's nothing.
[LENA growls softly]
Inside now, mister.
[ACE]
Yes, ma'am...
[ACE] She said she was gonna
buy me some ice cream
as a thank you.
You can't really call
that a date, can you?
I don't think that's the most
pressing issue here,
is it, Ace?
Y-Yeah? Okay, what's up?
Huh? [gasps]
Oh, wow!
Where'd that come from?
Talk about bizarre!
What is it?
Don't play dumb!
[laughs] I found it floating in
the ocean, near the breakwater.
I've never seen
anything like it!
[gasps softly]
[ACE]
Wonder what'll hatch.
[LENA]
N-O spells no, mister!
It might've been
my imagination,
but I could've sworn I heard
it calling out my name!
We're running a
café slash grill--
there's no way we
can keep a pet here.
Do you get what I'm saying?
Yes, ma'am...
[LENA] Now take it back
where you found it, okay?
[ACE] I was really hoping
I could keep it.
[KING] We can go
find monsters together,
once you're a little
older, I promise.
[ACE]
I wish...
[gasps]
This guy's about to hatch!
What should I do?!
Am I supposed to try to
keep it warm, or--?
[gasps]
Huh?
Drops?
[roars]
[OPERATOR A]
Drop Impact confirmed, sir!
[OPERATOR B] Scanners indicate
it's a dragon-type monster.
Located two clicks
north of area B-9.
Then let's try to keep
him out of the city!
Deploy gates B-8
through 10!
It's exactly like
Adjutant Nudo predicted.
DFS Barrier! Activate!
[COMMANDER YAMAKI]
Your foresight comes in handy
once again.
The evacuation of the remaining
residents is in its final phase.
Once we've been given the
green light to stage an attack
against the creature with live
ammunition, it could get messy.
Just make sure that
no civilians are harmed
in the operation.
That would be unacceptable.
Understood, sir. I'll be in
the command center preparing.
Collateral damage to
the surrounding structures
seems unavoidable,
wouldn't you say?
Which could affect the
mayor's next election.
Your words, not mine.
Yes, of course, Commander.
[SDF B] Please head to the
central plaza for evacuation.
There's food and water...
This is the final
group to evacuate!
[SOLDIER E] Good! Time to
leave it to the SVO team.
We've been given orders
to fall back
to Rally Point Bravo as well.
[CO A]
Let's get moving!
[SOLDIERS]
Sir!
[ACE]
What's going on down there?
Target moving out from B-3!
AFS Tank 2!
It's moving towards you!
Can you see it?
It's closing in!
Where? I don't see--
[grunts]
Target sighted!
[TANK COMMANDER A]
Astro-Particle Cannon! Fire!
We knocked it down, sir!
Good! Turn on the Anti-Rave!
[LANCE] Hmph.
Guess his element's fire.
[DEVI]
It's just a stray, Devi!
The big oaf doesn't even
have control over himself!
[LANCE] You're right.
Let's show him the way back.
--[ACE] Hey, show-off!
--[DEVI] Devi?
Make him stop right now!
Using monsters
to wreck the place,
what's the matter with you?!
Devi.
Yeah, the kid's got our egg!
[ACE] Well?
Why don'tcha say something?
Whatever you do, don't
let it out of your sight.
[DEVI]
Devi!
[ACE]
Wait! Come back!
[DEVI]
Hey, listen!
And just you might
learn a thing or two!
Now pay attention, Devi!
Don't be afraid. I've come
to ease your pain--
I'll be quick.
[yells]
[LANCE]
Calling my monster allies.
I command you by
our ancient agreement,
and the right granted
by my blood.
Unleash your might on
my enemy and bring him down!
Release!
[roars]
Is that monster with
the Dragon Caller?
It is indeed!
He absorbed the Drops!
Right! He transferred
Drop Power to it.
[gasps] Wait,
you can see them, Devi?!
[screeches]
Game over.
It's time for you to leave.
Idiot.
Here we go--
[gasps]
Well, that's no good, Devi!
What's no good?
[DEVI] There aren't enough
Water Drops to pull from!
Drops come from the
elements found in nature,
but the boss is surrounded
by a bunch of buildings
and energy shields!
[ACE]
So... he needs more Water Drops?
Drops...
What are these?
[gasps]
That kid...
Did he do this? He formed these
Drops from that distance?
Huh...
Well, well...
Drop Surge!
[DEVI]
Five combos, Devi!
I knew there was more!
I'm coming, Boss!
Devi!
It's near.
Time for a good
old-fashioned Boss Fight!
[DEVI]
Armor Drop, ready!
[LANCE]
Prepare yourself, Devi!
That monster's gigantic!
Dragon Lord Zaerog Armor!
Cross-On!
[DEVI] Master Lance,
you were as cool as ever, Devi!
I can't wait to Cross-On
the Soul Armor, Bossman!
[VOICE] Yours truly will be
coming up huge, Tama!
[DEVI]
Who's "yours truly"?
[BOTH]
Next time:
--"Cross-On" Tama!
--"Cross-On" Devi!
[VOICE]
Ace'll lend a helping hand, too!