[TIGER]
What's going on?!
That's weird!
Uh? What?
[TIGER grunts]
This one's cold!
This one's cold, too!
Same here!
Cold! So Cold!
The hot springs are all cold!
You don't need to jump
into each one to find out.
Maybe all of these pools
are supposed to be cold water.
That ain't it!
These soaking pools should be
piping hot like all the rest!
Life as we know it
will never be the same!
It's cold?
I guess that means we can't
make soft-boiled eggs, tama.
[TIGER]
If I can't bathe in splendor...
[TIGER] ...how can I
hope to go for the top?
You're more bummed out
about these hot springs
than you were about
failing the Guild Exam!
Which is insane.
[CHARO]
Besides, it's just a bath.
Just a bath?!
What exactly do you think
traditional baths are all about?
Soaking in hot water
for hygiene?
Heaven never made one
hot water better than another!
--Huh?
--[TAMAZO] Tama?
It's a saying we have
back home in Geyser.
It doesn't matter who
you are, or who you hate,
or how much you
might despise them,
once you take a relaxing bath
together, everyone's family!
I believe world peace
can be achieved
through socializing in the buff!
I don't know, taking
a bath with a bunch
of total strangers
sounds awkward.
Besides, I usually
just take a shower.
No way! Are you kidding?
A shower could never stack up!
[groans] Kids today
just don't get it!
[CHARO growls]
Hey, I'm not just a kid!
[TIGER] And nothing's as good
as drinking ice-cold milk
after a nice, hot bath.
[MILK VOICE]
Boop!
Well, it's hard to get kids
to appreciate the simple things.
[CHARO] Would you stop
calling me a kid, already?!
This is pretty strange.
There must be some reason
it isn't hot anymore.
[SECRETARY A]
Master Eldora?
Guild Dragon Caller Garnet
is here to see you.
Master Eldora. Greetings!
How have you been?
What can I do for you?
[GARNET] I just did a
PR concert here in Geyser,
so I dropped by to say hello.
It's nice to see that
you haven't changed.
And it looks like I could say
the same about the room.
[gasps] That sword has
Geyser's emblem on it!
How cool!
I always wanted
something like this...
[ELDORA]
Please don't touch it.
[GARNET grunts]
All right...
Did something happen
out there and I haven't heard?
The city seems so restless.
[ELDORA]
Are you done?
Huh?
I've got a lot
on my plate today.
Would you mind
seeing yourself out?
[door creaks]
[sighs]
[ACE]
Scalding Bath. Electric Bath.
Mineral Bath. Waterfall Bath.
Sulfur Bath?
Wow.
I had no idea there would be so
many different types of baths!
Pump the brakes, dude.
Are you telling me
this is your first time
to visit a hot spring?
Yeah, I've seen 'em on
travel shows on TV,
but we didn't have any
back in Vienna City.
[gasps]
I wonder what that is.
What's with all the ruckus?
All of the town's
hot springs have gone cold.
Huh...?
We found those pools outside
town that were cold, too!
This has never happened before.
[SULFUR BATH OWNER]
I don't know.
Maybe the Ancient of Fire is
starting to lose her power?
Hush! Don't say
things like that!
If she heard what you said,
you'd be in real trouble!
[FOOT BATH OWNER]
I heard from my butcher,
who heard from his cousin's
neighbor that she wants to
turn this whole area into her
own personal spa facility.
I've called the
office several times,
and she's too busy to answer!
She must not care about
the good the hot springs
do for our community.
Who's Eldora?
Is she the Ancient of Fire?
Yeah, that's right.
[TIGER]
Hey, pops!
Huh? Hi, Tiger!
Have you heard? All of the
hot springs have gone cold!
Ah, yes.
It sets my mind to wonderin' if
something might've happened
to the monster down at
the secret hot springs.
Secret hot springs monster?
[ELDER]
Yes!
The heat source for these
local springs isn't geothermal.
Instead, they use the monster's
energy to make these bath houses
the best on Dragoza.
Then where is this
secret hot spring?
[ELDER] There. You'll find it
at the foot of that mountain!
Right! Let's roll, gang!
What? Isn't it a little too far?
Let's go, Charo.
We shouldn't just stand around
if we can help these people out!
Ace! You're a real
stand-up guy, you know that?
I Love you, bro!
[ACE laughs]
Okay. Okay, I get it!
Fine, I guess we'll go.
[TIGER]
Off to the secret hot spring.
And untold adventure we go!
[ACE] Tamazo.
What did you bring?
Eggies, tama.
I'm going to make yummy
soft-boiled eggs
as soon as we get to
the spring, tama!
[ACE] You're really into
soft-boiled eggs, huh?
I had a realization after
eating them in the hot spring.
Soft-boiled eggs have
practically unlimited
potential, tama!
Unlimited potential?
[TAMAZO]
Just think about it, tama.
I've seen soft-boiled eggs
on top of noodles, curry,
even salad! You can put soft-
boiled eggs on anything, tama!
They're the Double-A
batteries of the food world!
Taste explosion!
Tamazo, they say the ones
who talk about it the most
know the least.
Tama?
[TIGER]
Raw eggs are where it's at!
Steaming hot rice.
Raw egg. Soy sauce!
And... [pants] ...tasty!
I'm a sunny-side up
kind of guy.
And my mom makes the best
sunny-side up eggs
in all of Vienna City!
Put some ketchup on it, and--
[BOTH yell]
[TIGER] Ketchup on
sunny-side up eggs?!
Talk about barbaric!
[TAMAZO] You should put salt
on sunny-side up eggs, tama!
[TIGER]
No, soy sauce!
No, Ketchup!
[CHARO]
Do we have to talk about this?
I'm starting to get hungry.
[ACE] Sure, raw egg
on rice is great,
but sunny-side up
is just better!
[TAMAZO]
Soft-boiled eggs, tama!
[TIGER] Raw eggs and rice is a
dish that has been enjoyed
by people for centuries!
[ACE] Yeah, well,
sunny-side up is a classic, too!
[TAMAZO]
Soft-boiled eggs, you fools!
[ALL scream]
[TAMAZO]
Soft-boiled eggs rule, tama!
[CHARO]
Would you just drop it already?!
[ALL scream]
[ALL panting]
[ACE] Didn't we see that same
exact flower a little while ago?
[CHARO]
Did we loop back around?
[ALL]
Hmmm...?
Hey, hold on just a second.
You do know the way,
right, Tiger?
[TIGER grunts]
Tell me you know the way.
The elder told me we could find
the hot spring at the foot
of the mountain,
so I just started walking
in that general direction.
So you're saying you don't know
where the secret hot spring is.
Well, it is a secret hot spring!
If I knew about it,
it wouldn't be secret, would it?
[groaning]
[whimpers]
What gives?
I don't much appreciate those
sideways looks, you know!
That's too bad!
Just because I decided
to come out here without a map
and got us lost, you think I'm
some kind of idiot, don't you?!
Your words, not mine.
[groans]
I'm so hungry.
I barely have the strength
to take another step!
Me, too.
At least we still have the eggs
Tamazo brought with him.
Wait a minute! Your pack
suddenly seems a lot lighter!
[TAMAZO] I got a bit peckish, so
I ate a few along the way, tama.
[ALL scream]
[ACE]
Only one egg left...
The precious belongs to Tamazo!
You already ate plenty,
you greedy egg hog!
Ah-ha! It's mine!
[TAMAZO]
Give it back, tama!
[TIGER] You've had more
than your fair share!
[sighs]
Everybody just chill out--
[gasping]
[gasps]
See what you've done?!
You've gone and killed us all!
Are you seriously trying
to put the blame on me?!
[CHARO]
You better believe I am!
You brought us all the way out
here without knowing the way!
I don't care about some
dumb hot spring anymore.
You girls really know how to
give a guy an earful, don't ya?
Oh, come on, I'm not a girl!
[ACE]
Hey! Can you guys hear that?
[water rushing faintly]
[TIGER]
The secret hot spring!
I can't believe we found it!
Ya-hoo!
Look, guys!
[TIGER]
It's a monster!
A Salamander. He's a fire type.
[gasps] That's weird.
The flame on his back is gone.
[TAMAZO]
Tama?
[CHARO] This
is a crime scene!
[BOTH gasp]
[TAMAZO] And so the three Guild
Exam failures stumbled upon...
...The Mystery of the Hot-Spring
Monster Murder!
[dramatic fanfare plays]
[CHARO] Usually, Salamanders
have big, blazing flames
like this on their backs.
So what happened
to make him like that?
[gasps]
[BASUDORA roars]
[ALL grunting]
[GARNET]
Finally found you guys!
I couldn't call you
on your D-Gear,
so I tracked you
down from above!
Uh.
Whoa, hold on!
He's alive, but he's
looking pretty weak.
Huh?
We can save him, if you
give him mouth to mouth!
No, thank you.
Why don't you do it?
[CHARO] I've never heard of
anyone resuscitating
a monster that way!
[TIGER] Monsters and humans
aren't so different.
We both have nostrils, right?
[TIGER] I think it's
worth a shot at least.
--[CHARO] No.
--[ACE] What do we do?
It's twitching!
Okay! Salamanders are
fire element, so that means
if you feed him Fire Drops,
he might get his energy back!
All right then! If we all
work together we-- Garnet?
Sorry, but I've got
places to be.
I'm sure you guys
will figure it out!
[ACE]
Uh! Hey, Garnet! Come on!
Let's try to get
him back on his feet!
[TIGER]
Cool, we're on it!
[CHARO]
Yeah!
[SECRETARY]
Oh, you're back!
No, Miss Garnet.
You have to wait!
What is it?
You've made one visit
just to say hello already.
[GARNET]
Just this!
[ELDORA sighs]
I know about the
whole thing, Eldora!
Do you?
Rumor has it that
someone wanted to turn
Geyser's hot springs
into a spa facility
the likes of which this
world has never seen.
Salamander, this city's
heat source, refused.
So she attempted to murder him.
[GARNET] As he lay there
on the verge of death,
he somehow mustered enough
strength to scrawl a message
about his attacker.
He drew Geyser's
emblem with his claw!
And the only person allowed to
wear this emblem
is the Ancient of Fire.
Which would make you
the murderer!
[sighs]
Are you finished?
[gasps]
Am I wrong?
Of course you're wrong, Garnet.
That sign was there to
keep Salamander asleep.
It was basically a seal.
So that's it?
But why'd you have to make
him sleep in the first place?
Because something was
making Salamander angry.
If he went on a full rampage,
all of the hot springs
would've dried up
and this town would be
ruined in the process.
[MAN A]
The hot water's come back!
Even if the seal is broken,
it shouldn't matter.
Salamander's slumber
will remain undisturbed
until someone feeds him Drops.
[GARNET squeals]
[ELDORA] Now let's go
and restore the seal.
What's the matter?
[GARNET whimpers]
We may have a bit of a problem.
[SALAMANDER chomping]
[CHARO] Looks like he's
got his strength back!
[ACE]
Yeah. We did good!
[TIGER] And the hot spring
is back in action!
It's so busy!
Now this looks like
the Geyser I know!
Why don't we hit up the baths?
And we can keep looking until
we've found the hot spring
that suits you best!
Yes!
Hey, Tiger! Come try out
our Scalding Bath house!
It's hotter than hot, and really
helps soothe sore muscles!
[TIGER sighs] My friends aren't
really old enough for this one.
I mean, that is
ridiculously hot!
I think I'll pass.
But how long does it take
to cook a lobster in there?
--Give it a try!
--[yelps]
[TIGER screams]
I've been flash-fried!
What's a Spin-Cycle bath?
[yells]
[ACE]
Tiger!
It's a hot spring that de-grimes
your body automatically.
You look like a trophy, tama!
[LUKE-WARM BATH OWNER grunts]
There we go.
Man, what a busy day.
[SALAMANDER growls]
[ALL]
Snack-time chow down!
Soft-boiled eggs
are delicious,
but so are these
sweet steamed buns!
[SCALDING BATH OWNER]
What's the big idea?!
I've got your mineral
water overflowing
into my Scalding Baths!
[MINERAL BATH OWNER]
The water's surging!
I can't help it if it flows
onto your property!
Can we do something
about that stinky sulfur?
Don't sully the
good name of sulfur!
We're the most
popular bath in town!
What? Our bath is more popular!
[TIGER] Come on, you guys.
There's no need to fight!
[BOTH] I don't recall
asking you, Tiger!
[yelps]
[ACE] Don't worry!
We're coming for you, Tiger!
You humans' hot springs
are so foolish.
[OWNERS yelling]
Say what now?
[SALAMANDER growls]
[ACE] Whaddaya mean,
"humans' hot springs"?
[ELDER] Originally, there
was only one hot spring here
in the Fire City, operated by
a local Dragonoid fellow.
Hearing about his success,
humans from all over
began moving here,
seeking their fortunes.
Each opening their
own hot spring bath.
Every time a new one opened up,
Geyser's cityscape
and the surrounding terrain
were irrevocably changed.
[ELDER] Now they're
constantly competing to prove
their bath house is the best.
Which leads to further
land development.
[ACE sighs]
[OWNERS yelling]
It looks like the
Salamander's gone!
[ELDORA]
We were too late.
[D-Gear beeping]
[GARNET]
Come in, Ace! Where are you?
[ACE]
At the hot springs in Geyser.
[GARNET] The Salamander's
heading your way!
You have to stop him
before he gets to the city!
[SALAMANDER hisses]
There he is!
He looks super mad, tama!
Why, though?
It'll be a disaster if
he makes it to the city.
Who knows how many
people he'll injure!
It's all up to us, then.
Easy there, Tiger.
He must have some reason.
Maybe so, but I have
to protect my town!
[SALAMANDER growls, hisses]
Now! Release!
Let's Rock 'n Roll, Agdrall!
[AGDRALL growls]
Cross-On!
[yells]
Cross-On, tama!
Oh! Awesome!
[SALAMANDER hisses]
[ACE grunts]
[TAMAZO yells]
Oh no! Are you okay?
[ACE, TAMAZO groan]
[growls]
[SALAMANDER hisses]
He's so strong!
[SALAMANDER roars]
[TIGER yells]
[grunts]
[SALAMANDER hisses]
[TIGER yells]
[TIGER, AGDRALL groan]
[SALAMANDER hisses]
Ah! Tiger!
I'm not letting you
through, you got it?
Eat this! Quad Combos!
[AGDRALL yells]
[SALAMANDER grunts]
[ACE]
He's going back.
The heat for the hot springs
comes from a monster?!
And you defeated him, Tiger?
Yeah! Did it with one hit!
[LUKE-WARM BATH OWNER]
Why'd you go and do that?
Huh?
Now all of the hot springs
are back to being cold water!
Tiger!
Why don't you think about the
city before you act next time?
I didn't mean to...
[CHARO] Everything he
did was for this city!
Charo.
Tiger cares a lot more
about this city
than any of you loudmouths!
Why don't you ask yourselves
which you care about more,
this city or your wallets?
[TIGER groans]
[CHARO]
You've made a mess!
"Heaven never made one hot
water better than another!"
No matter who you are,
or who you despise,
I thought that once you take a
nice, relaxing bath together,
everyone's supposed
to be like family!
In our quest for customers,
we ruined the hot springs
without realizing it.
[OWNERS sigh]
[TIGER]
Nothing is ruined yet!
[OWNERS gasp]
I swear, we'll all be back
in our baths again soon!
[OWNERS sigh]
[SALAMANDER hisses]
[CHARO]
The Salamander's come back!
Run for your lives, people.
Hold on! Something's different.
He doesn't want to fight us.
I'm not sure what's wrong.
[SALAMANDER hisses]
I have a feeling
he wants to evolve.
Huh?!
[SALAMANDER growls]
[IFRIT roars]
[CITIZEN A]
All right!
[CROWD MEMBER B]
The hot springs are back again!
[roars]
[CHARO] The Salamander
evolved into Ifrit!
But Ace, how did you
know what it wanted?
I'm not really sure. It was
almost like... like I felt it.
Oh, wow.
Tama?
[ELDORA] You were able to
calm the Salamander's rage,
and noticed he needed
to evolve into Ifrit.
I'm quite impressed by all
that you've accomplished!
Allow me to extend my gratitude
on behalf of the people
--of our city.
--[cheering]
Master Eldora, why don't you
come enjoy one of our baths?
Yes! I'd love to!
[cheering continues]
[GARNET sighs]
[TIGER]
Okay! Off to the baths we go!
[TAMAZO]
It's about time, tama!
[CHARO]
We did have quite a workout.
[gasps]
What?!
[CHARO]
What?
You mean, you thought I was
actually a girl this whole time?
[TIGER]
Yup.
[ACE] I'll admit. I made
the same mistake at first.
[CHARO]
Really?
[TIGER] Don't worry
about it, little buddy!
Either way, you've got
guts and heart!
That's what counts.
[gasps]
Who's up for some
soft-boiled eggs?
[GARNET] I didn't know
you smiled, Master.
[ELDORA] Of course I do.
This is part of life in Geyser.
These hot springs are
important to the people.
And as long as it makes
them happy, then I'm happy.
[GARNET]
Mm-hmm.
That Ace boy, he seems
a lot like his father, King.
You know about King?
Can you tell me about him?
Sure.
He was a brave Dragon Caller who
could understand the feelings
of his monsters.
I guess Ace takes
after his father.
[SECRETARY]
Master Eldora!
What is it?
[SECRETARY] It's an emergency!
You need to come quickly!
[gulping]
[sighs]
Yummy, tama!
[CHARO]
Oh, yeah! That was perfect!
[TIGER] This is the stuff
we Geyser-ites live for!
[CHARO]
Heh, we should visit again!
[ACE]
Agreed!
[TIGER] Yeah. I'm sad to
leave my home behind,
but I'll definitely
come back one day.
[BOTH]
Huh?
We're a good team!
I figure I might as well tag
along with you for a while!
Together, we can
go for the top!
--[CHARO] What?
--[ACE] Are you serious?
Now that that's all
been settled, where to?
Man! I'm so excited!
Goin' for the top
on a global scale! Whoo-hoo!
[CHARO] Rule one of traveling
with us:
you have to stop roaring
and yelling like a maniac
all the time!
[ALL laugh]
[D-Gear beeping]
[ACE]
Hey Garnet.
[GARNET]
Is Charo with you?
[CHARO]
I am.
[GARNET] The Ancient of Wood
isn't doing well,
and Libria's in
some serious trouble!
What?
What's this Libria place?
It's my... my hometown.
Bad news.
[TIGER] They say Charo's
hometown is in real trouble!
I don't really understand all
this "Ancient's post" business,
but I'm positive we'll
figure it out eventually!
Next time!
"Wood City Libria."
You know I'm gonna be double
gung-ho next week, too!