[NARRATOR]
For untold centuries,
there have been powerful
warriors who fought against
the various crises that
threatened our world.
They harnessed
the power of the monsters,
and forged a bond which
eased the planet's anger.
They were the Dragon Callers.
[NARRATOR] Dragon Callers
are born with the special power
to bridge the gap between
the realms of nature,
mankind, and monsters.
When fear and hatred contaminate
the elements that surround us...
...the Dragon Callers will
rise up with their monsters
and restore balance
to our world.
Another mission well done!
Guess you've gotten the
hang of this line of work
faster than most others do.
In fact, you're starting to
build quite a reputation!
For real?
That's pretty cool.
That is cool!
And it's all thanks
to Tamazo, tama!
Whatever you're doing is
working, so please keep it up!
--Sure!
--Tama!
[CHARO]
Ace! Tamazo!
Charo! Tiger!
Reporting in the
completion of your mission, huh?
Is that what
you guys are doing here?
Yeah.
It's not easy being a full-time
Dragon Caller for the Guild.
We decided to
take ourselves a little break
here in Libria.
And I thought this
would be a great opportunity
to drop in for a
visit with Torlie.
Oh. Him.
The Ancient of Wood?
I wanted to say hello
and see how he's doing.
Tiger decided he would
tag along with me.
You wanna join us, too?
Sounds fun!
Of course, I will!
Tama will tag along, too!
Charo?
[CHARO]
Hi, Torlie!
[ACE]
Hello!
[TAMAZO]
Tama, tama.
Hello, everyone!
Welcome back to Libria!
What's the deal
with that big backpack?
Are you moving somewhere, sir?
[TORLIE gasps]
Oh, this?
I'm just
heading into the forest.
[TORLIE] I heard a lot of good
things about you boys.
That you're all
working really hard.
Yeah! After all...
...we carry the future of
the Dragon Callers' Guild
on our shoulders, don't we?
Right now, you're
carrying me on your shoulder!
--Tama!
--Wasn't talkin' literally.
But please, tell me honestly:
Was it all right that we
asked to join you, Torlie?
Yes, of course!
Plus, this gives you the chance
to see the forest spring!
And I don't mind
having the company.
[ACE gasps]
Wait. Drops?
[CHARO]
Huh?
There, you see 'em?
Dude, you're right!
Think it's a Drop Impact?
No, that doesn't
seem like what's happening.
Yeah. There aren't
enough Drops for that.
Once I became the
Ancient of Wood,
a lot of things
needed my attention...
...but I finally
managed to catch up,
and I decided to visit the
spring since it's been a while.
Look! More Drops, tama!
It's just as I thought.
There are more.
[GROUP gasps]
This forest has areas
where Drops surge into existence
like water welling
up from a spring.
But recently,
I've heard rumors that the
amount of Drops is on the rise.
Do you think it's
some sort of sign
of the next Drop Impact?
I haven't
reached any conclusions,
but it certainly seems
to be some kind of
recurring phenomenon.
Ah. Tamazo.
You're strangely quiet.
What're you doing?
I'm catching a big one.
Do what now?
[TIGER]
Huh? Woah.
Hey guys it looks like
he's fishing with his tail!
[screams]
Your nose caught one, tama!
And he's a big 'un!
You're a real angler, tama!
It may not be all that much,
but please help yourselves!
--[ACE] Sure!
--[GROUP] Thanks for the food.
[TAMAZO]
Tama, tama, tama!
Fantastico!
And even better, because it's
being shared by our friends!
Yup!
Still, seems kinda strange.
You're the Ancient:
Can you just suddenly leave
the city and go camping?
[TORLIE] If something's
wrong with the forest,
I need to figure it out.
It's the most
important part of my job.
I have to keep Libria safe.
Glad to hear it.
It really takes a burden
off of my mind to know
that my hometown is under your
watchful protection, Torlie.
So, will the amount
of Drops in the forest
keep increasing?
Well... I'm not sure.
The spring is the water
source for all the plant life
in the area.
I hope I'll be able
to find something there,
but unfortunately, it may end up
being quite the long shot.
The spring's water is
the life source of the forest.
We have to try.
Yeah.
Wow. That's complicated, but I'm
picking up that we need to do
whatever we can to take care of
this spring, is that right?
[TAMAZO giggles]
Way to use your noggin, tama!
[laughs]
Yes, and that's
my main reason for going,
but it's also because of this!
Wait, what?
That must be
Master Tinbell's Egg Drop!
Master Tinbell and I
first met one another
when I was
investigating the spring.
I used to travel from
one end of Dragoza Island
to the other for my
archaeological research.
[gasps]
Is that another Drop Impact?
It must be.
[TORLIE] Drop Impacts were
randomly occurring all across
the island, and when
compared to older reports,
they were occurring
with greater frequency.
But why was that?
What was causing it?
To find the answer I needed,
I came to this forest.
Beautiful!
[TINBELL] You mean,
you can see the Drops, child?
[TORLIE gasps]
[TORLIE] That's when
I first met Master Tinbell.
What are Drops, anyway?
And how do they transfer their
energy to the monsters?
Have you ever
considered such thoughts?
Yes.
I've been on expeditions
researching just that!
Drops are nature's
power manifested
in the atmosphere.
A limited energy
that is generated
from within the world itself!
[TINBELL]
Correct.
Try to think of it
as the blood of this planet.
Drops are blood?
Then there must be a reason
we've had so many Drop Impacts.
Because this planet's been hurt.
It's wounded.
[gasps]
So, then if that's the case,
the planet's using its
blood to heal itself.
And since
it's so badly wounded,
these attempts to heal itself
are causing Drop Impacts.
And this sudden
increase in Drop Impact
frequency demonstrates how
badly our planet has been hurt.
That's bad news!
What if... What if
this situation continues,
and all of the Drops are used
up, what happens then?
Then this planet will die.
[GROUP gasps]
[growls]
Come with me, my boy.
[TORLIE]
With Master Tinbell's advice,
I became a Guild Dragon Caller.
After passing the test,
I returned home to Libria,
and Master Tinbell said to me:.
"Continue pursuing
your archaeological studies,
and find a way to stop the world
from tearing itself apart."
So, then what happened?
You found a way?
No.
Too bad, tama.
Well, it wouldn't
be a big problem
if it was easy to fix.
Right. But I won't give up!
I'm going to do my best,
and give it everything I've got.
I know you will.
[ACE]
Hmm? Can't get to sleep either?
No. What Torlie said earlier is
bouncing around in my head,
and I just can't stop thinking.
Oh, yeah? About what?
All of the Drop Impacts.
If they're natural occurrences
meant to heal this planet,
well, then that must mean
the monsters rampaging
because of Drop Impacts...
...are actually victims, too.
[gasps]
That's true.
But there's got to be
something we can do, right?
Some way to stop it
that we haven't tried?
You mean the Drop Impacts?
Yeah.
[ACE]
Hmm...
I wonder if
this planet really is dying.
How sad...
Huh?
I don't want something
like that to happen.
Same here,
but there's no need to worry.
Huh?
We've got Torlie
working on our side, after all!
And If anyone can find a way
to stop Drop Impacts,
it'll be Master Torlie,
the new Ancient of Wood!
Yeah. Sure.
Charo?
So early, tama.
Toyceratops, Dryad, Enju!
Go!
Mornin'!
Ace?
That was amazing!
Were we too loud?
Sorry if I woke you.
What are you up to
so early in the morning?
When I woke up, I felt
like I had to do something,
and I thought we could
use the training.
--[ENJU tweets]
--[TOYCERATOPS grunts]
Right on!
Mind if I join you?
No thanks, tama.
I'm still sleepy.
Tamazo!
Torlie was supposed
to meet with Master Tinbell
at the spring. It was fate!
Torlie's my hero,
and I wanna be just like
him when I grow up!
Of course!
And you can. I know!
Thank you very much.
[ACE gasps]
--Whoa!
--Drops everywhere!
There're more than yesterday.
Let's go!
Come on, now. Wake up!
[TIGER]
I'm gonna go for the top again!
[roaring]
[CHARO gasps]
That roar!
This way, tama!
This must be the
forest spring that Torlie
was telling us about!
Yeah!
That roar came from him, tama!
[roars]
[TIGER]
Ace! Charo!
Tiger!
So, the Drop
abnormalities did
originate from this spring!
[ACE gasps]
This guy is a wild Fortoytops.
Wait, a Forky?
No, a Forty-toy-a-what now?
He's the evolved
version of a Toyceratops.
[CHARO]
Toyceratops?
[roars]
[ACE] Why does he look like
he's in so much pain?
Hypothetically,
consuming too many Drops
might've led to this condition.
He could be suffering
because his energy level
is past its natural limit.
[roars]
[GROUP gasps]
Mega-powerful, tama!
[TORLIE]
He has to release that energy.
One way or another!
Let's end this!
Okay!
[CHARO]
Please, not yet!
[TAMAZO]
Tama?
This is the spring
where Torlie met Master Tinbell
for the first time.
Let me be the one to defend it!
But Charo...
Now's not the time to show off!
Don't be so quick to doubt him.
Have a little faith
in your friend.
[gasps]
[CHARO]
My monster allies...
Help me fight those
who stand against us!
Let's go! Release!
[roars]
Toyceratops!
Enju! And Dryad!
Come!
[ENJU tweets]
[TOYCERATOPS growls]
[gasps]
[ALL screech]
[CHARO gasps]
He's strong!
You can say that again!
That Forty-Torty-something-
or-other monster is being
a total pain!
[CHARO gasps]
Did he hurt you?
Please don't be injured
because of me!
Can you stand up?
[TOYCERATOPS groans]
[CHARO]
Are you all right?
[TOYCERATOPS growls]
[ACE]
Charo!
I can't turn away!
It's time to give
him a hand, tama!
[roars]
He's crying.
This poor Fortoytops
is just a victim, too.
I'm going to do my best,
and give it everything I've got.
[CHARO]
Right now, I'm powerless.
I can't save this planet,
my hometown,
or even this forest, and yet...
[CHARO]
...I want to save you!
I still can!
[FORTOYTOPS roars]
[roars]
Poor Charo.
Ah! Hey! You still
need to watch your back, dude!
I think I understand the
way Charo is feeling right now.
You do?
That failed...
I failed...
Everyone can return.
[gasps]
But why?
Uh... How're you gonna fight
without your monsters?
[TIGER]
Okay, I think I get it!
He's gonna hit 'im
with some Fire Drops!
Charo.
[gasps]
Water Drops?
He's got it mixed up, tama!
It's Fortoytops's skill.
[TORLIE] He can turn Water Drops
into Heart Drops.
[gasps]
Charo!
Thank you, friend.
[CHARO]
You understood.
I was just trying to help.
I'm a Guild Dragon Caller,
and my duty is to restore the
Drops to a state of balance.
[CHARO] I would never do
this just to hurt monsters.
[FORTOYTOPS sighs]
I promise,
and of course, it takes time...
...but I swear...
...I'll make this forest
just like it was.
[gasps]
Uh... Tops?
Good news, guys!
I think that Tops
understands me!
It sure looks that way.
Always had faith!
I never doubted you
for a second, Charo!
[CHARO]
Yeah, I can see that.
[ACE]
Honestly, I was worried.
Try not to be so reckless!
[CHARO] I'm not afraid
to do something like this
because I know you guys
will always have my back!
[TAMAZO]
That's what teamwork is, tama!
[ACE]
Yup!
[TIGER]
We do have your back.
You can count on that.
[TIGER]
Far out!
[ACE]
Your own Soul Stone!
He accepted you, Charo!
[CHARO]
He accepted me?
For real?
[TIGER] Yeah! Old Fortinbras
really liked you!
[TORLIE]
Charo, I'm very proud of you!
The Drops are dissipating.
Soon, it will all be
back to normal.
[CHARO] Does that mean
the forest's problems
will start to fade away?
[TORLIE]
Yes!
[TAMAZO]
Well, c'mon!
Let's make that
Soul Stone shine!
Awm! Tama!
[TAMAZO]
Armor Drop, Tama!
Here you go!
[CHARO]
Thank you, Tamazo.
[TAMAZO]
Tama.
[ACE]
Well? What's it look like?
[TIGER] It's time to rock
your new Soul Armor!
[CHARO]
Heh! Right!
Fortoytops!
Lend me your power!
[CHARO]
Cross-On!
[TIGER]
Wow!
[ACE]
That's cool!
[TAMAZO]
Looking so fresh, tama!
[CHARO]
It's almost like.
I can feel the
Fortoytops's soul!
[TORLIE] One day, we may
have another burst of Drops
to deal with here.
And next time,
it might trigger a Drop Impact.
--It's great!
--Yeah!
--Cool!
--Is the head heavy?
[TORLIE]
And yet... there's hope.
These children are
the key to our future.
And they won't face it alone.
I'm not letting this
planet die, either!
Please watch
over us, Master Tinbell!
We need it!
[TIGER]
Tiger here!
Born and raised in
the Fire City Geyser,
I live a life of
reaching for the top,
and having fun hanging
out with my buddies!
[TIGER] But then, a certain
someone shows up.
Next episode:
"Tiger's Tough Time."
I have my own path
to walk in this world!