[NARRATOR]
For untold centuries,
there have been powerful
warriors who fought against
the various crises that
threatened our world.
They harnessed
the power of the monsters
and forged a bond which
eased the planet's anger.
They were the Dragon Callers.
[NARRATOR] Dragon Callers are
born with the special power
to bridge the gap between
the realms of nature.
Mankind and monsters.
When fear and hatred contaminate
the elements that surround us...
...the Dragon Callers will
rise up with their monsters
and restore balance
to our world.
[CHARO]
Hey! Look, I see it!
That truck down there!
[ACE]
Huh?
[ACE] Guess those military guys
decided to keep him
in their fort.
Let's mount a rescue!
Huh?
Don't you "Huh?" at me!
He's their prisoner!
Who knows what kind of horrible
things they're doing to him?
How can you not be worried?
I thought he was
your friend! Poor guy...
[TAMAZO whimpering]
[EVIL DOCTORS
laughing maniacally]
[maniacal laughter continues]
[whimpers]
[EVIL DOCTOR cackles]
[TAMAZO screams]
[CHARO whimpers]
[ACE]
Hmm...
Stop that!
I'm so happy!
Sure, I'll help!
Question... Tracking
him down is one thing,
but how are we even
supposed to get in there?
I'll come up with something,
don't you worry about that!
Oh...
[CHARO]
Hmph!
[LANCE] I understand there's a
captured monster
being held here. Hand him over.
Hang on. Are you that
famous Dragon Caller?
You're Lance, right?
Well according
to this form here,
we haven't caught
any monsters lately.
Perhaps you're mistaken?
[NUDO]
Hmm...
Waah!
[phone beeping]
[gasps]
Hear that?
What's that noise?
Devi...
Devi!
[LANCE]
He wasn't there.
Devi--?!
[grunting]
[LENA]
Oh, my! Here.
[LANCE] I went right
where you told me to go,
but he wasn't there.
[DEVI gulping]
Ahh!
That's not possible, Devi!
[LANCE]
Are you certain?
[growls]
I can still feel the presence
of that bargain-brand wannabe!
I'm sure! He's in
that base, no doubt!
He's in what base?
Don't tell me Ace is off
trying to infiltrate the SDF.
I dunno anything about that!
Of course.
[phone beeping]
[LANCE] So... how long are you
going to just sit around
eating their food?
These are the best sunny
side-up eggs I've ever had!
Once I start snacking,
I just can't put it down, Devi!
[phone beeps]
[CHARO] Huh... Something
tells me those guards
aren't going to
let us go strolling
right through the front gate.
Probably not.
But don't you worry!
I'll devise a plan!
[BOTH gasp]
I'm here to pick up the dirty
uniforms for dry-cleaning, sir.
Yes. That's it!
[CROWD MEMBER A]
You're the best!
Thank you!
[CROWD MEMBER B]
She's so cute!
[METAL]
Another top-notch show!
We've got ten minutes
of down time scheduled.
And after that,
it's time to hit the road.
Thanks, ten!
Jeez! Lame!
[bones popping]
There were barely enough fans
to make the show even worth it!
It's so freaking annoying!
I know you've got
the monster here!
My power as a Dragon Caller
draws me to it!
If you insist on lying,
I'll have to report such
flippant behavior to the Guild.
It's my understanding you were
ordered to capture that monster.
And since that didn't happen,
you've come here casting blame.
You certainly have a
brash attitude for a man
who clearly failed the
mission assigned to him.
You're a nuisance,
you know that?
Irresponsible fools like
yourself come here,
bringing havoc to this town
and countless others like it.
We've heard from the Guild.
They're going to send us a
representative of the Ancient.
We will hand it over then.
We will not give it to you.
[LANCE]
Hmph.
[COMMANDER YAMAKI]
Was that the wisest choice?
What could we possibly gain
from handing the monster over
to some bare-footed
young buck?
If we hand it over to the
Ancient's representative,
then the Guild will
owe the SDF a favor.
And that kind of favor is
worth the property damage
the town sustained.
[RECEPTIONIST] Is there
something I can help you with?
I'm a Dragon Caller.
I must see the mayor regarding
an issue I have with the SDF.
Take me to him.
Huh? Uh...
[RECEPTIONIST]
Bare foot?
Right. Then you're going to
want to hold onto this ticket
and then wait right over there
for your number to be called.
[LANCE]
Eighteen.
[ACE, CHARO grunt]
It looks like we're in!
An update on the
status of the monster:
King's son has
infilitrated the facility
and is bound to make contact.
[SONIA]
Very well.
I will continue to
monitor the situation.
Wow, this place is enormous.
We just need to narrow
down our search area.
You can count on me!
There we go.
Now we'll use the
SDF base map I found online
to give us a better picture.
This corner is where
we're hiding now.
[TAMAZO]
Ace. Ace!
Hmm? His voice.
I heard it.
Huh? Whose voice?
I didn't hear anything.
Sounded like... it came
from that building!
Tama?
Push!
Tamamamamamamama! Push it!
Tama, Tama! Push it!
[TAMAZO laughs]
[muffled] This one is
exceptionally buttery,
but it lacks a
certain sweetness.
I've certainly had better.
Ahm! Mm-mm!
This one has a nice sesame
and salt seasoning, Tama.
The flavor really grows on you!
Now! Time to help Ace!
Ace! Come and find me!
Huh?
[CHARO]
Hmm?
I think he's in the basement.
Basement, huh?
But how can you be so certain?
Because when he
was just an egg,
he called out to me in the exact
same way, and I found him.
He called out to me then...
...like he's calling me now.
Then the only remaining
problem is getting inside.
[TAMAZO]
To the left, Tama!
Ah. The left?
Hey, look at this air vent.
You think we can get in?
Oh, yeah! Great idea!
[FEMALE RECEPTIONIST] Next!
Number 18, calling number 18!
And how can I
help you today, sir?
[LANCE] Take me to the mayor.
I'm a Dragon Caller.
Profession... Other. There!
So, what particular municipal
administration issue
for the greater Vienna City
area is your visit regarding?
Huh?
[FEMALE RECEPTIONIST]
I think your best bet would be
to head to the
City Planning Department,
it's down on the third floor.
Try the Disaster
Prevention Department.
Fourth floor.
[DISASTER PREVENTION DEPT]
Monsters, huh?
Sounds like an Animal Shelter
kinda job to me.
Or maybe the
Public Health Department?
They're in Building C,
fifth floor.
Generally, the purview of
our department is not
monster retrieval services, sir.
Since this is such an
unprecedented case,
you're going to have to
contact the mayor directly!
We don't even have the paperwork
for this sort of transfer.
I've been telling you
bureaucrats to let me speak
to the mayor since I got here!
[ACE grunting softly]
[gasps]
[ACE] Hey!
Which way do we go now?
I can tell you. Just let me
look it up real quick.
You know, statistically,
you're more likely to find
your objective by veering
off to the right.
[TAMAZO] Over here.
Follow my voice, Tama!
[ACE] Hmm. Sounds like
it's coming from the left.
You don't say...
Hey, Charo! Do you think
you can open this up?
I think so. Yeah,
it shouldn't be a problem.
According to his directions,
this is our stop.
Wow, so you actually hear him
giving you directions?
Sure... ish.
--[METAL hums]
--[knocking]
Yes? What can I do for ya?
Well you might've noticed
we didn't have much
in terms of an audience
at the last show.
But this next one's gonna
be different, isnt't it?
Don't you worry about a thing,
it'll be all right!
We'll have a full house
this time, I'm sure of it!
Who wouldn't want to see
a singing, dancing superstar?
[GARNET giggles]
Stop it, you're making me blush!
You ol' smoothie, you!
[panel clatters shut]
[GARNET hums]
[CHARO]
Great. The coast is clear.
Hey, hold on, Charo.
He's saying not to
make a move yet.
Wait five seconds.
Okay. Not only are you
hearing which way we should go,
you're also avoiding
guard patrols now?
I'm not really sure
how he knows it.
I just listen to what
he's telling me.
[LANCE] I need to
speak with the mayor.
Of course, please take a number
and wait for it to be called.
Ninety-nine?
Are you kidding me?
[bells chiming]
[gasps]
[ANNOUNCER]
Morning office hours are over.
City Hall is now
closed for lunch.
We look forward to serving
you again at 1 PM.
We found it. He must be in
that room under lock down.
But there are guards
at the door.
I know.
[TAMAZO]
Tama... Tamamama...
[groans]
[farts]
[SOLDIER B]
Gas? [coughs]
[SOLDIERS coughing, retching]
[SOLDIER D]
We deserve hazard pay!
What's going on?
[ACE] Don't know,
but this is our chance!
[CHARO]
Is this it?
[ACE]
Uh-huh.
There!
[CHARO]
It's no good! The door's locked!
Ace, hurry! We have leave
before the guards come back!
[ACE growls]
I know! I'll use Drops!
[growls softly]
What's wrong?
Just come out! I can't!
[TAMAZO]
Don't give up yet, Tama!
[gasps]
I'll help you out.
You'll help me?
Tama.
--[ACE grunts]
--[TAMAZO growls]
[TAMAZO]
Tama...
[ACE]
I can feel it!
[ACE gasps]
[CHARO]
That. Was. Incredible!
[pop music plays]
Hey, guys!
It's show time!
[GARNET] ♪ If you're
feeling sad and lonely, ♪
♪ and you find all you wanna
do is curl up and hide away! ♪
♪ Maybe-- ♪
--[alarm pinging]
--[PAGE SYSTEM] Emergency.
Emergency. A monster
in the special cage unit
has escaped
from confinement.
Nearby personnel are to
report to the area immediately.
I repeat...
Not now! We don't
have time for this!
[PAGE SYSTEM] ...in the special
cage unit has escaped
from confinement.
Nearby personnel...
[COMMANDER YAMAKI]
Hey, wait!
Stop! That's off-limits!
You don't have access!
[door opens]
Uh?
[SOLDIER E] Huh? What, sir?
There's an intruder?!
Hey, you! You're not
getting one step further!
[beeps]
[LANCE]
Release!
[AOYAIBA growls]
Whoa! What the--?!
[CHARO]
There!
Now we just have to
figure out which button
to press to open it up!
But which one is it?
Hit the one
on the right, Tama!
The right one?
[CHARO gasps]
Hey, uh... I just
thought of something.
When your friend over there
told us to hit the button
on the right,
do you think he meant
we should hit
the button on our right?
Or the one on his right?
His right.
[alarm blares]
[ALL gasp]
[growling]
[BOTH gasp]
Time to run!
Yeah, I agree!
[TAMAZO]
Tamama!
[CHARO wails]
[PURPLE MAJILU snarls]
[CHARO whimpers]
[SOLDIER G]
Hold it right there!
Huh?!
[gasps]
[PURPLE MAJILU snarls]
[SOLDIER G whimpers, grunts]
[ACE, CHARO panting]
Run for it, Tama!
--That's what we're doing!
--We can't all fly!
Zoom, zoom, zoom!
[growls]
Hey, get back here!
Where d'you think you're going?!
[gasping]
[growls]
Huh--? [grunts]
[SOLDIER J]
That's not good.
[grunting]
[SOLDIER J whimpers, yells]
[growls softly]
[GARNET] ♪ You don't
have to think of me, ♪
♪ if you just be yourself ♪
[GARNET]
Don't interrupt!
♪ Look around
and you'll see! ♪
♪ You have friends who want
to stay by your side ♪
♪ to the end! ♪
Yay! Thanks, guys! Your
support means everything!
Wow, did you see that?
Miss Garnet is so strong!
Wham. Bam. Done.
Now's our chance!
Let's get outta here!
--I'm right behind you!
--[GARNET] What?
An encore, you say? Ha, ha!
[ACE] Me, a Dragon Caller?
Get serious!
[CHARO laughs]
I am serious!
I think you've got
exactly what it takes!
Someone with your kind of
power can't just stay here!
My power?
Even if I went to Dragoza,
they don't just accept anyone
who shows up, do they?
No, but Ace, you should.
You have a ton of potential,
but you need the training.
You have to become one!
Have to become one what?
You have to work to become one
of the protectors of our world!
Protector.
Exactly! So that's why you
should come to Dragoza Island
with me, and then we can both
study to become Dragon Callers!
There's a ferry that goes to
Dragoza Island tomorrow morning,
so I'll be waiting for you
down at the pier.
I have faith you'll be
brave enough to come!
See you then!
Ah--!
[laughs]
[TAMAZO]
Tama.
Protector...
[TAMAZO]
Tama, tama, tamama,
--tama! Tama-mama!
--[LENA sighs]
Tama!
You came for him, didn't you...
...Tamazo?
[TAMAZO] T-T-T-Tama,
Tama! Tama, tama.
Tama, Tama!
[ACE]
Come on. Where did I leave it?
You looking for something?
[ACE yelps]
It's okay to want to go.
It's strange.
I spent so much time worrying,
helping you out,
and running errands.
But then, I realized something.
And now... I know... I...
I was trying to
find my purpose!
Now I know.
I have to leave home.
So... I'm going
to Dragoza Island.
[ACE]
I have to...
[LENA]
Ace!
I'm proud.
Goodbye, dear.
[gasps]
--[LENA grunts]
--[ACE sobs]
Work hard...
[ACE] I will! I swear!
I'll study to be the strongest!
That way... I can protect you.
I have to protect you!
[whimpers]
You're just like him.
Train to be strong, but real
strength comes from kindness.
And kindness is a power
that you already possess.
[ACE whimpers]
Tama.
[LENA] You'd better take good
care of him, Tamazo.
T-Tama!
I'm glad you
decided to join us!
Honestly, I was afraid
you might get cold feet.
But I guess I
was wrong, wasn't I?
Guess so.
[LENA]
Say hi to Grandma for me.
Just so you know, Grandma can
get really scary sometimes.
[ACE]
Serious?
[LENA]
Please, Ace, be careful.
[gasps]
[TAMAZO]
Tama? Ooh!
Whoa! [laughs]
So cool, Tama!
[ACE] Would you please
keep it down, Tamazo?!
[TAMAZO] Bidding farewell
to his homeland,
Ace embarks on a grand journey,
and meets new people.
Lucky guy gets a brand
new monster, too, Tama!
Next time!
"Dragoza Island," Tama!
That new monster better
remember who was here first.