[NARRATOR]
The Battle Cup,
where ambitious young Dragon
Callers come to compete against
one another and determine
who's the best of the best.
It's a high-stakes tournament
where matches are fought
based on fighter classes.
They're all competing
for the glory,
as well as the Golden Egg.
The late Ancient of Light,
Master Lukes, banned Soul Brave,
an ancient Dragon
Caller technique.
However, that ban was lifted
by the current Ancient
of Light, Master Jest.
Utilizing their Soul Armor
and various monsters,
these Dragon Callers are aiming
to bring home the big win!
Ready yourselves, challengers,
for the moment of truth!
Get ready!
To the top!
Here I come!
God Burning Attack!
[TIGER grunts]
Hang in there, Entetsu!
[TIGER screams]
Heh, heh.
I suppose we can get started
now. Go on, Zeus.
Wrath of God!
[BILLY yells]
With that attack, Starjohn
secures victory!
Starjohn will advance
to the second round!
[CROWD cheers]
[METAL]
And after a short break,
we'll get the second round
of matches underway!
[ELDORA] I wonder if lifting
the ban on Soul Brave
was really the wisest choice.
[VAHATON]
Hm... You know,
I was thinkin' the same thing.
But it was rather exciting
to see Ace pull off
that Soul Brave. It was almost
like watching King fight.
I'm against the decision.
It's unfair, and it's dangerous.
[DAFNES]
The law of nature dictates
that the strong will win.
However, I'm not as
worried about a rookie
using Soul Brave as I
am about Starjohn.
[JEST]
What do you mean?
If something were to go awry,
we could end up losing
one of our Dragon Callers
in this tournament.
Well, the Battle Cup was
a live-or-die tournament
for the Dragon Callers
of yesteryear.
In such a high-stakes struggle,
certain concepts like fairness
cease to be relevant issues.
Besides, even if what you fear
may happen were to
actually occur today,
we'll only lose human
Dragon Callers.
[gasps]
[DAFNES] And that's why
I'm saying it's dangerous.
Oh, my. It appears
the Ancient of Dark
has grown quite soft
of late, hasn't she?
[CEO 5A]
Garnet, sweetheart,
you can do that Soul
Brave thingy, right?
At least give it a shot.
We're talkin' mega-endorsements
if you do!
Well, to start with,
it's dangerous,
and before today, I've
only ever read about it!
[CYNTHIA]
Master!
Uh?
When did you get here?
"Master"? Hey, who is this kid?
I attend the academy where
Master Garnet graduated
top of her class!
Did you come out here
to cheer me on?
Well, of course I did!
As the Chairwoman of
Master Garnet's Battle Cup
Cheering Squad, I just
couldn't miss this!
[CEO 5A]
Uh... Uh?
Huh?
I promise to cheer you on
with everything I've got!
[CHARO]
Ace!
That Burning God Attack was
brilliant, how'd you do it?
And can you teach me?
I can't really explain,
it just sorta happened
on its own, you know?
The Soul Brave alone was great,
but then you broke out
that killer finisher!
You were totally awesome, Ace!
And he never could've
done it without help
from his ever-faithful Tamazo!
Don't go fishing for
compliments, Tamazo.
[laughs]
Here I am, feeling nervous
about being in front of all
those people out
there in the stands.
How about you? Do you
ever get nervous?
Not really. I've never really
stopped to think about it.
Huh?
I don't know what'll
happen next,
but I'm really lookin'
forward to round two!
Wow.
You and I are very different.
Mister! You're my hero, sir!
Could I please get
your autograph?
[AGET]
Soul Brave, huh?
I'm not trying to
get hurt out there.
Maybe I should withdraw?
Let's see, my opponent in
the next match is Charo?
Of course!
She's the little girl that was
palling around with Tiger!
There's no way she
could use Soul Brave.
I can do this if
it's just a kid.
I can win!
[laughs]
Charo! You're fighting
Mister Aget next, aren't ya?
Yeah, that's right!
You know, I squared off
against him once before,
and Mister Aget's justice
is extremely powerful!
[AGET laughing]
He's cackling like
a madman, tama.
I wonder what was so funny?
[TIGER]
Charo!
Think of it as Mister Aget
giving you a sparring lesson!
And give it your best shot!
Yeah!
[ANNOUNCER 29A] Battle Cup
round two will begin shortly.
Registered Contestants,
please set your D-gears
and head to the stage.
Okay, this is it.
Come on! Let's give it our best!
Uh. Give it our best...?
All right!
[CYNTHIA]
Break a leg out there!
I just know you'll make everyone
back at school proud!
Back at school... Uh...
The academy was where our
paths first crossed.
The long-standing thorn
in my side, Valkyrie.
[inaudible]
Now let's go win this match!
[CROWD cheering]
[METAL] Are you ready
for the second round,
ladies and gentlemen?
[CROWD cheers]
Mister Lance!
Good luck out there!
[DRAGON CALLER 29A groans]
[METAL]
Good gravy!
Only ten seconds in,
and Lance has already
claimed victory
over his opponent!
He's too tough for you,
cupcake! See ya later!
Devi, let's go.
[DEVI]
Uh. Hey!
Wait for me, Master Lance!
[METAL] And with that win,
Lance from Class A
is moving on to round three!
[CROWD cheers]
Mister Lance is like,
incredibly strong!
He certainly is.
What the--?
Huh?
[HARU]
It's Ace. What's he doing?
What's this now?!
Over in Class C, Ace's opponent,
Logan hasn't shown up yet.
Do you think he's just trying
to steal the spotlight
by arriving fashionably
late, tama?
What a snob, tama! Ha!
You think that's
what's going on?
[TAMAZO] We'll put you out of
your misery soon enough!
Tama, tama!
Class C match up, round two!
The mighty Dragon
Caller hero, Aget,
faces off against
Libria's own Charo!
[AGET] Are her monsters
really all Wood element?
I can beat her in
two seconds, flat.
But, it would be a real shame
to finish this match
off so quickly.
I stand now before you,
the great Dragon Caller:
Me, Aget!
[CHILDREN cheering]
[METAL]
Aget, the Dragon Caller hero,
is quite the popular personality
among the younger set.
Check it out!
This chiseled form!
The sinewy poetry of absolute
physical perfection!
Oh, man! What a gun show!
It seems like he's
gotten even stronger
since the time I fought
against him back in Vegahs!
Charo, try to keep your cool!
[CHARO] All of Aget's monsters
are fire element!
In Class B, round two starts
with Garnet versus Klein!
[CROWD cheers]
[gasps] Oh, no.
Ha.
[GARNET]
He's really handsome!
[GIRLS shrieking]
Wow. Isn't he just so dreamy?
Yeah! Let's go, Garnet!
[FAN 29A]
We've waited for you!
[FAN 29B]
You're our superstar!
[MAN 29A] But if this Garnet
girl is really such a celebrity,
how come Klein seems to have
so many more fans than her?
[MAN 29B]
She might be a celebrity back in
the real world, but he's clearly
got the upper hand here.
Let's get started!
It's time to Cross-On!
[METAL] Garnet is sporting
her Valkyrie Soul Armor!
Facing her is Klein,
with advanced Dragon
Caller's Soul Armor!
[MAN 29A]
Hang on.
I thought you needed to have
a monster's Soul Armor
if you wanted to use Soul Brave?
[MAN 29B] So I guess that means
Klein can't activate Soul Brave.
It's not that I'm incapable.
I just choose not to.
I don't see the
point in expending
all of the extra energy if I'm
merely fighting a human female.
Huh?!
[KLEIN]
I'll show you all that humans
will never be a match
against we Dragonoids!
[GARNET]
That uppity attitude of yours
is getting really annoying!
Release!
[GARNET]
[HERRIOT]
Garnet,
don't let that jerk get to you.
You can crush him!
Here you go, Green Troll!
Earth Enhancement!
[GREEN TROLL roars]
The Earth Enhancement skill
increases wood attribute
attack power!
[gasps]
Mermaid!
[METAL]
Though they've just started,
Garnet is already losing ground.
Can Klein keep this up long
enough to pull off a win?
Oh, jeez!
This Battle Cup stuff is scary!
It looks like our star's
in a real bind!
It's time for us
to pump things up!
Yeah!
All right! Let's go, guys!
[FANS]
Yeah!
[FAN 29A]
Ready...? Now!
[FANS]
Garnet! Garnet!
Garnet! Garnet! Garnet! Garnet!
[gasping]
[FANS]
Garnet! Garnet! Garnet!
Garnet! Garnet! Garnet! Garnet!
Thanks, you guys.
What are they doing?
How absolutely heavy handed.
Huh?! Who do you think you
are?! Those are my fans!
[gasps]
[chuckles]
[GARNET]
His monsters are wood elements.
I can give Naga
Fire Drops, and then...
Heh, heh.
Ha!
[METAL]
After using his leader skill,
Klein's attack has now
tripled in strength!
[GARNET gasping]
[GARNET screams]
[CROWD murmurs]
[METAL]
This doesn't look good!
Garnet isn't getting up!
Will Klein claim
victory over her?
[GARNET grunting]
Not yet.
Poor Master!
[FAN 29A]
Garnet!
[FAN 29B]
Don't push yourself!
That's so adorable.
Your little pod of fanboys
are crying over you.
You really shouldn't build up
your fans' hopes so much
before you let them down.
Heck, you should probably
just give up now!
Let's make this clear:
I might be a Dragon Caller,
but I'm also a singer!
And this is my stage, where
my devoted fanbase and I
can sparkle together with
everything we've got!
[applause]
We aren't done here.
I won't quit now!
Valkyrie!
Attack stance... Light!
[METAL]
A bold move!
Valkyrie's skill changes any
Heart Drops over to Light Drops!
[METAL]
This battle's far from over!
Garnet returns fire!
[GARNET grunts]
Yay! Way to go, Master!
[yells]
[FANS]
Garnet! Garnet!
Pesky girl!
[grunts] Machine Storm!
Rolling Geotight!
[HERRIOT]
Machine Storm's skill
enhances all available
Wood Drops, huh?
If this keeps up--
[gasps] Is she planning
something?
[GARNET screams]
[gasps]
[GARNET groaning]
[METAL] Klein ruthlessly
lands blow after blow!
[KLEIN] You're rather
stubborn, aren't you?
Let me finish this.
Come, Earth Knight!
Guard Break Strike!
[EARTH KNIGHT roars]
[METAL] Garnet is unable to
block the incoming attack!
[CYNTHIA]
Please, you have to stop this!
[FAN 29A]
I can't watch anymore!
[FAN 29B]
Leave Garnet alone!
[panting]
Come on, guys.
I thought you were
rooting for me?
Huh?
[panting]
The show's just getting started!
You don't wanna miss it!
Naga! Menace!
[gasping]
[METAL] Naga's skill prevents
the opponent from moving!
No! I'm rooted to the spot!
[GARNET]
Everyone, come back!
Wait, she isn't actually...
Valkyrie.
I made a promise to you
that we'd sparkle together.
Now please, Valkyrie.
Will you connect with me?
This stage is all ours,
now let's get to work!
[GARNET]
Soul Brave...
...Valkyrie!
[gasps]
What's Garnet doing?
[HERRIOT] She's not fighting
for her own sake.
This time, she's
finding the strength
to fight for someone else.
Uh? Miss Herriot?
That emotion connected with
Valkyrie on a deep level.
That emotion...?
That's right. My guess is
she's fighting for those
who've always supported her.
[GARNET]
Here we go!
[METAL] Incredible! Garnet's
Soul Brave is spectacular!
Wow. Amazing!
[CROWD cheers]
[METAL]
She truly is
the strongest celebrity
Dragon Caller!
[METAL]
There it is! The Cross Drop!
It can't be! [growls]
[yells]
Prism Feather Sword Attack!
[KLEIN screams]
[panting]
Thank you!
For everything!
This one's for you!
[CROWD cheers]
[FANS]
Garnet! Garnet!
Master!
[METAL] Garnet moves ahead
to the third round!
[groans] I can't believe
I was beaten by a human.
[AGET]
Hmph.
The cool hero of justice!
[groans]
[AGET]
Plop...
[METAL] Charo advances
to the third round!
[CROWD cheers]
I just won.
Dude! You defeated Mister Aget!
You're amazing, Charo!
[TAMAZO]
How much longer, tama?
[ACE] I'm startin' to get
really tired of waiting.
[METAL] Surprisingly,
Ace's opponent, Logan,
has yet to make his appearance.
Maybe he got spooked after
Ace used Soul Brave,
but who could blame the
guy for being scared?
Well, what happens if
this opponent of his
doesn't ever show up?
Then Ace is the winner of
the match by default!
If so, then it looks like his
next opponent is going to be...
[gasps]
What's the matter?
If his opponent, Logan,
fails to show up,
then Ace's next match is...
[laughs]
[HARU]
...against Charo!
[CHARO] It's been my dream
to become a Dragon Caller,
and entering the Battle Cup
was a dream within a dream!
But me being here
definitely isn't a dream.
Next time:
"Our Friendship Battle."
Ace, let me show
you how I fight!