[NARRATOR]
The Battle Cup,
where ambitious young Dragon
Callers come to compete against
one another and determine
who's the best of the best.
It's a high-stakes tournament
where matches are fought
based on fighter classes.
They're all competing
for the glory,
as well as the Golden Egg.
The late Ancient of Light,
Master Lukes, banned Soul Brave,
an ancient Dragon
Caller technique.
However, that ban was lifted
by the current Ancient
of Light, Master Jest.
Utilizing their Soul Armor
and various monsters,
these Dragon Callers are aiming
to bring home the big win!
Ready yourselves, challengers,
for the moment of truth!
This is it!
You really made it, Ace!
You're in the final
battle against Lance!
And how cool is that, dude?
You did a great job,
and you should be proud!
[ACE] "Did"?! Why are you
talking in the past tense?
The battle hasn't
even started yet.
[laughs]
You're right, man.
Sorry about that.
You think we're going to lose
this fight, don't you, tama?
No, you must've
misunderstood me, dude!
I bet it'll all work out as long
as you have a strong heart!
You just give it your
best and go for broke!
Well, I wasn't
planning on losing.
I'll do everything
I can to win this!
[BOTH]
Wha--?
Wait, what's up?
See? These guys do
think we're gonna lose.
Come on, man, give us a break.
You know that's not true!
Yeah, what he said!
We totally have faith
you'll win this thing, Ace.
Your face looks funny when
you're telling a lie, tama.
Oh, I know! Let's go
and talk to Miss Herriot
before your match begins!
Because, she's fought against
Lance a number of times,
and might even have some
insights on him to give you,
if we ask her!
Great idea! Hey,
nice going, Charo!
So, whaddya think, Ace?
Sure thing!
[HERRIOT] You're asking me
for a way to beat Lance?
That's right.
Does he have any weaknesses,
or maybe some hidden tricks?
I don't wanna goof up like you.
[HERRIOT]
I didn't goof up, kid!
[TAMAZO] So we don't embarrass
ourselves out there, then.
Are you morons trying
to pick a fight?!
Do you think I'd look like this
if I had that kind of info?
No, guess not.
[HERRIOT]
Try using your brains next time!
Come to think of it,
Miss Herriot has never
defeated Lance in any
of their previous battles.
If she's always lost to him,
how's she gonna give us
advice on winning?
Master didn't just lose
to him, he crushed her.
Now would you simpletons
please stop rubbing salt
in the poor woman's
wounds, already?!
You just hurt my feelings
worse than they did.
[whimpers]
Oh. I'm really sorry.
This whole thing is my
fault, Miss. I apologize.
[sighs] This squishy little
guy is just so darn comfy!
I'll forgive you boys
if you leave Eggy here.
You're heavy!
I'm not a pillow, tama!
This is our chance
to get outta here.
Right on.
Hey, do you have any idea why
a bunch of us Dragon Callers
refer to Lance as
the "Prince of Ice"?
[ACE]
Uh, no.
[TAMAZO] Is it because he
grew up in Ice City, tama?
No, that's not it.
It's 'cause he always
has his guard up.
When you're in the
midst of battle,
you can usually get some sense
of what your opponent
is feeling.
Anguish, joy, fear,
those sorts of things.
With Lance, I was never able
to get any kind of
read on that kid.
He remains cool under pressure,
and stays frosty on defense.
I see. So he really
earned that name.
Yeah. Bottom line, I don't know
what to expect from him,
let alone any specific
weaknesses he has.
But Ace, the most
important thing
isn't what your opponents
weaknesses might be.
It's about taking advantage
of your own strong
points in a fight.
If you can boost your attack
with Horus' multi-color-combos,
you might just stand
a chance against him.
[gasps]
Stay true to yourself and
the rest comes naturally.
That's the best
advice I can give.
Staying true to myself?
Right! Then get all
fired up and--!
[groaning]
[GARNET]
Master!
[TAMAZO]
Take it easy, tama!
Thanks a lot, Herriot!
I appreciate it!
[BOTH gasp]
I get that Lance is pretty
strong, but I don't care,
'cause I have my monster
friends to back me up!
I'll believe in
what they can do,
mixed with me giving
it all I've got!
Tamazo's with you
all the way, Ace!
Oh, yeah!
All right!
Good luck out there, kid!
[laughs] Thanks!
I can't believe Ace
is fighting Lance
for the Battle Cup championship!
It's all so exciting!
I don't even know which one
of them I should cheer for!
That's easy.
You Keep cheering for Ace.
He's become the pride of
Vienna City, after all.
If he beats Lance here, he's
going to become super famous.
I just hope he'll remember
all the little people
that helped him get where he is.
[LENA grunts]
Uh? Back in his younger days,
King used to lose
matches all the time.
[gasps]
[ANGENE] I even worried that
he didn't have what it takes
to be a real Dragon Caller.
I guess I never knew that.
Oh, yes. Well, he was
actually quite pitiful.
So, no one knows what the
future has in store for Ace.
Any mother would fear the worst,
but the sorts of things they
worry about seldom happen.
I don't that think Ace
is going anywhere.
I hope you're right.
And of course, nothing could
keep King from losing to you.
I-I don't know what
you could mean.
His father lost to me, too.
[BOTH laugh]
I wish you the very best
in your match, Lance.
Thanks.
The boy, Ace.
Master Vahaton holds the
abilities of that young man
in high regard.
Don't take him lightly.
You may need to unleash
everything you've got
on him in order to win.
Right.
But Soul Brave takes
a toll on the user,
both in body and spirit.
It's dangerous if you push
yourself too hard.
And you sometimes
have difficulty
remembering your
own limitations.
Yes. I'm aware.
Now, ladies and gentlemen!
The final match of the Battle
Cup is about to begin!
Ace, from Class C, defeated his
adversary in the last round,
which gave him the right
to battle against Lance,
from Class A!
Who will win this
year's tournament?
Will it be the reigning
champion, Lance?
Or the challenger, Ace?
[CROWD cheers]
There he is.
Good luck, Ace!
Here we go.
Give it your best shot!
You might even get lucky!
Don't get beaten
by some show-off!
Go, Ace! Go for the
top of the Battle Cup!
I never thought the final
round would be against you.
Yeah, what Master Lance said!
I can't believe you
made it this far!
We'll see if you have
real power, devi!
This isn't gonna go down
like the Guild exam.
I'm not a rookie Caller
tryin' to pass a test.
I came here to win!
Ha! You can talk that bunch
of smack all you want, devi!
We'll show you that you're
no match for us, devi!
Don't underestimate us!
We're gonna whoop you until you
cry "boo hoo hoo devi," tama!
You've got rotten
egg-spectations!
I'm gonna crack you open,
and devour you on a bed
of steamed rice, devi!
[TAMAZO] Ahh... Heaven
is raw egg on rice, tama!
It's the finest dish in
the whole world, devi!
Wait. We're not supposed
to be bonding, devi!
--Stop talking, Devi.
--[DEVI] Devi.
--You too, Tamazo.
--[TAMAZO laughing]
Well, it appears as if
both sides are ready.
Without further ado,
let's get this final
Battle Cup match started!
Cross Fight!
[ACE]
Cross-On!
Cross-On, tama! Hi-yah! Ha!
Oh! Awesome.
[yells, laughs]
Yeah! Devivebub, go!
It's time for Soul Brave.
Horus!
[HORUS squawks]
Answer my call, Zaerog.
Use Soul Brave!
[ZAEROG roars]
Both contestants have
used Soul Brave!
Looks like they're planning to
start this battle at full power!
[grunts]
[yells]
You're too slow!
Then I'll try again!
[LANCE grunts]
[yells]
[CRYSTAL AURORA DRAGON roars]
[ACE grunts]
He chose to block
my first attack.
I guess he was just trying to
see what I was bringing.
Now, he won't even let me
close enough to touch him.
Right, guess I'll take my turn.
[yells]
[screams]
What raw power!
With one stupendous blow,
Ace is knocked to the ground!
[CROWD cheers]
Oh, no!
Too bad, there's no hope!
He's done for.
[TIGER, GARNET, CHARO growl]
Lance pulled that off well.
Harnessing Drop energy seems
to come as effortlessly
to that young man as breathing.
Lance has been able to read
the flow of the Drops
since he was little
more than a toddler.
That sort of talent is quite
uncommon, even among Dragonoids.
Well, when you put it like that,
things aren't looking
too good for Ace.
But this battle's
barely even begun!
And Ace never would
have made it this far
if all he had was blind
luck working for him.
I'm interested to see
how a mere human
compares to Lance's
natural talent.
[ACE groaning]
[TAMAZO]
Are you all right, Ace?
I'm fine, but man, Lance
really packs a punch!
But I'm not going to lose.
I'm going to win!
Let's do this. Go, Ouka!
[roars]
Activate your Inferno Blast!
[OUKA roars]
[yells]
[gasping]
[ACE]
No way.
I thought I had him for sure!
That attack was sloppy,
your speed is a joke.
Crystal Aurora Dragon!
[CRYSTAL AURORA DRAGON growls]
Unleash Blizzard Blast!
[roars]
[CRYSTAL AURORA DRAGON roars]
[ACE screams]
Ace just took Lance's
attack full force!
The damage must be massive!
Will Ace be able to get back up?
He has to!
If I know Ace, he's
not out of this yet!
It's over. That attack
had to have hurt a ton.
He's like two seconds
away from giving up.
Would you can it with
the sass, already?
Okay, Johnny?
Johnny?!
[CHARO]
Seriously!
Ace is trying his hardest!
And no one needs your sour
attitude here, Tommy!
Charo's right, Bobby!
[DONNY] I told you a buncha
times, my name's Donny!
You guys're only gettin'
the "O" and the "Y" right!
Let's go, Ace! Wake up!
Don't you tell me that this
is the best you've got!
Stop slacking and get back up!
You can do this, Ace! Show
that punk what you're made of!
[groaning]
[TAMAZO]
Ace!
[FRIENDS cheering]
--[CHARO] Come on!
--[TIGER] You got this, Ace!
[GARNET]
You can't quit on us yet!
Everyone...
[TIGER grunts]
[TIGER groans]
Hang in there, Entetsu!
I can keep fighting!
I can't lose like this.
I refuse to!
I won't lose, do you hear me?!
What a remarkable turnaround,
Ace is back up on his feet!
Looks like everyone's cheering
really helped him out!
[CROWD cheers]
[DEVI]
Ha! You can't get anything done
without other
people's help, devi.
I couldn't have come all this
way if it weren't for them.
I'm even stronger
because I have friends!
How ludicrously naive.
Oh, yeah?
[yells]
Ace dishes out a
barrage of attacks!
Will Lance be overwhelmed?!
How marvelous.
Exactly the kind of
push Lance needs
to draw out his
fullest potential.
You're up...
...Tamazo!
Oh, yeah! You got it!
Gungnir! Ha!
Odin Tamazo's Gungnir
spear lands on Lance!
Did any of the damage
make it past his defenses?
Armor Skill. Eye of Wadjet!
Oh, it's on now!
He's gathering up four
different types of Drops!
Which means his attack
has been boosted 12-fold!
It's time, you guys!
[TAMAZO] Uh. He still
hasn't broken a sweat,
even after that attack!
[ACE]
How can we hope to beat him?
Stay true to yourself and
the rest comes naturally.
[ACE]
How do I do that?
Is this the extent
of your power?
I'm somewhat disappointed.
[ACE grunts]
Let's go, Devi.
[DEVI]
Roger that, devi!
Go! Hell's Charge!
Devivebub's skill enhances
all Dark and Heart Drops
in Lance's field,
and now Lance can recover
any health that he's lost!
Time to end this.
[yells]
[screams]
[ACE groaning]
No! Poor Ace!
I can't bear to watch!
[crash]
Lena.
Sonia.
This isn't right!
What has the Guild
done to my boy?
This is all according
to Ace's choices.
But--!
[SONIA] He's giving this
fight everything he's got.
He has to be able
to endure this pain
in order to become a
true Dragon Caller.
Go back.
[LENA whimpers]
[ACE groaning]
[panting]
[LANCE]
What now?
Are you ready to give up?
As long as I can fight,
I'll never quit!
Come, my monster allies.
I command you by our
ancient agreement,
and the right granted
by my blood.
Unleash your might upon my
enemy, and bring him down!
Come forth, Aoyaiba!
Mirage Blade attack!
[AOYAIBA roars]
[ACE screaming]
[METAL] Aoyaiba's skill
strikes Ace hard!
[CROWD cheers]
[ALL gasping]
Ace. Come on.
I think it's time for
us to end this fight.
Ace's body can't take
much more of this abuse.
It can't be helped.
Will you make the announcement,
Master Jest?
I feel that ending the match
now would be premature.
We should give Ace a little more
time to rediscover the power
that brought him to this point.
Are you certain?
Ace! No.
[ACE groaning]
I can still fight! I can!
You've suffered enough, tama!
You gave this fight
your very best, tama!
'Cause I have you
fighting at my side!
So I know... I can... win!
Ace! No!
T-Tama?
Time to stand back up.
What? Tamazo?
We can't call it quits just yet.
Now get ready, Ace, 'cause the
real fight starts here, tama!
[yells]
That's a surprise.
[ALL gasping]
Holy Moly! Ace is revitalized
with immense willpower!
Is this the true power of Horus,
the eternal bird, phoenix?!
[CROWD cheers]
[ACE]
I can still fight!
My power, my friends' power,
we'll put 'em all together
to beat Lance!
Right?
So, what's the problem, Horus?
Next time: "Intense Battle!
Lance Versus Ace."
I need more power!