[NARRATOR]
For untold centuries,
there have been powerful
warriors who fought against
the various crises that
threatened our world.
They harnessed
the power of the monsters
and forged a bond which
eased the planet's anger.
They were... the Dragon Callers.
[NARRATOR] Dragon Callers
are born with the special power
to bridge the gap between
the realms of nature,
mankind, and monsters.
When fear and hatred
contaminate the elements
that surround us...
...the Dragon Callers will
rise up with their monsters
and restore balance
to our world.
Release.
You called, partner?
Yeah, I can totally
handle this on my own.
I thought you'd
wanna have some fun.
[SUPER SPECIAL OUKA]
Hmph. Him, huh?
I'm pure evil! You think
you can defeat me?! [laughs]
It's combo time! And I'm here
to serve 'em up fresh!
[yells]
[BLACK DEMON groans]
[BLACK DEMON screams]
[ACE]
Heh. You could come at me after
a million days of training,
and I'd still send you packing.
[squealing, screaming]
Ladies, please.
Hey. It's our own fault
for being so heroic.
Get used to it.
You're right.
Sorry to have to interrupt you
in the middle of
an awesome daydream...
...but you're about
to fall off the bench.
[ACE yelps]
Thought maybe you should know.
Can we keep this between us?
[ACE]
So how's this all work?
I thought I'd start having cool
battles once I got my D-gear.
[CHARO] You've still got a long
way to go before that happens.
[gasping]
Transform, Tama!
Tama? Tama.
He's quite the little
showman, isn't he?
Heh. You ain't seen nothing.
Well, he'll keep
pulling the attention.
Until you Cross-On
with some Soul Armor
and make people take notice.
But, that's a pretty
tall order for a rookie.
I can totally Cross-On
some Soul Armor!
Hey, Charo, do you know
what Soul Armor is?
You haven't learned
about that yet?
Uhh...
[CHARO] When a Dragon Caller
equips Soul Armor,
they're able to use that
monster's Leader Skill.
Is that so?
There's only one way to
get a set of Soul Armor.
You're gonna have to go
to the Sacred Temple.
I gotta go where?
The Sacred Temple is a
dangerous place,
nestled atop Mount Linus,
with the most unforgiving
terrain in Crocus.
It's also called the
Dragon Caller's Tomb.
Because every foolish adventurer
who's dared to set foot
in the Temple has
ultimately perished from
one of its diabolical
booby traps.
No one who's ever gone
there has come back.
Man, that temple
sounds ultra-serious.
So the bottom line is, you
can't hope to get Soul Armor
unless you're ready to give it
everything you've got.
You better be willing
to risk your life
if you want to make
a good Dragon Caller.
[CHARO] Uh... That's a
little different from what
this info page I found says.
[TAMAZO] Sounds awesome!
Bring it on, Tama!
Mister Tamazo, you're quite
the ambitious go-getter!
Tamazo's not afraid
at all, Tama!
You should quit trying
to become a Dragon Caller
and start thinking about
managing Tamazo's touring show!
Yeah? Well, I'll show you!
I've got what it takes
to get a Soul Armor!
Yeah! Let's go!
[GARNET]
That's the end of my set!
Thanks for your
kind support, you guys!
Next up we have a monster
who's a singing and
dancing sensation!
Give a warm
welcome to Onigiri-lit!
[CROWD cheering]
[CEO] Such a breathtaking
show today, Garnet!
You were absolutely
radiant on stage!
Can it!
There wasn't a single person
paying the slightest bit
of attention to me.
Hey, hey.
These hayseeds
can't appreciate the level
of star power I'm bringing out.
I'm getting pretty sick of
the entire barnstorming scene!
I'm amazing.
I should have better gigs!
Well... How do I put it?
Why are you
standing like that?
Stop stalling and talk!
I'll be perfectly honest,
but you can't get mad.
Off-stage... you
aren't interesting.
That was a little too honest.
Miss Sango plays
the piano like a pro,
and is nationally
ranked in long jump.
She's started dabbling in
Cantonese cuisine,
and she also got her
commercial driver's license.
Get the picture?
Yeah, well, I have a
unique set of hobbies
--under my belt, too, ya know.
--Oh? Like what?
Um... I-- Really cool stuff!
Don't you worry.
I've got a few ideas.
[GARNET]
A jelly-dumpling eating contest?
Seriously?
[ACE] So. Which way
to the Sacred Temple?
I think that's it,
up there on the hill.
Doesn't look dangerous.
Maybe all the trials are
located nearer the temple.
Let's go, Tama!
[ACE]
Excuse me?
I'd like a Soul Armor, please.
[CHARO] I guess no one's
at home right now.
[TAMAZO]
Delicious, Tama!
[ACE] Oh, man. Looks like
someone lives here!
[CHARO] And they're
not good at cleaning up.
[TAMAZO]
So good, Tama!
[ACE]
Hey! Stop eating right now!
[TAMAZO]
But it's calling to me!
You can't just do
whatever you want, y'know!
We should come back later.
[TAMA babbling]
[CHARO] Sorry for the
intrusion, please excuse us.
[STAFF] We're still accepting
new participants
for the jelly-dumpling
eating contest!
So sign up now!
There's even an
amazing prize longed for
by the greatest of
Dragon Callers!
An eating contest
with a prize, Tama?
[CHARO]
What if you win the contest,
and the prize is Soul Armor?
[gasps] What if this is
one of the trials, Ace?
Could be! We can't
afford to lose, Tama!
I'll go get us registered!
Tama? Tama.
Tamazo?
[sighs]
[whimpers]
[growls]
[WOMAN gasps, grunts]
[TAMAZO]
Tama! Tama! Tama?
Tama...
[TAMAZO gulping, laughing]
[TAMAZO]
Tama, tama-tama-tama.
[stomach growling]
[TAMAZO]
Was that your stomach, Tama?
I was so focused on
cooking everything this morning
that I forgot to eat.
It was so scrumptious that
I ate the entire thing
by myself, Tama!
I'm very sorry about that.
--There's no need to apologize.
--[stomach growling]
--[gasps]
--Tama?
I might have an idea. I hope you
like jelly-dumplings, Tama.
Huh?
[HOST] Welcome one and all
to this year's eating contest!
Featuring Linus'
world famous jelly-dumplings!
--Look who just showed up.
--[HOST] The winner will receive
an extravagantly
luxurious prize.
[CHARO]
It's Garnet! But why?
Maybe the grand prize
really is a Soul Armor!
If that's the case,
we have to win this!
[HOST]
Ready? Set!
[TAMAZO]
Tama...
Chow down!
What is with these?
[whines]
[CROWD cheering]
[TAMAZO smacking]
[whines]
Keep munching!
[ACE]
[HOST] Who could've expected
such an entertaining
carnival of consumption?
Which of our top three
contenders will win?
Soft-in-the-head
monster Tamazo?
Singing, dancing, Dragon Calling
triple threat, Miss Garnet?
Or will they be beaten
out by local know-how,
courtesy of the underdog
contender, Miss Sally?
Currently between jobs...
Which of these powerhouses
will come out on top,
and take home our...
Awesome.
It's like he was born to it!
[HOST]
And we're done!
[whistle blows]
[HOST] The winner of today's
dumpling eating challenge...
Shaped like a dumpling
himself, it's Tamazo!
--[CROWD cheers]
--[BOTH laugh]
[HOST] And now, let's show
our champion what he's won!
It's what legendary Dragon
Caller Master Vahaton
calls his favorite treat!
An entire year's supply of
Linus' world-renowned
jelly-dumplings!
[TAMAZO] Oh, yeah!
Tamazo is super stoked! Hah!
[TAMAZO]
Tama...
[ACE]
You did it, Tamazo!
I do all right when I try.
[ACE] And if this is the prize,
I'm glad I didn't win.
I don't know how you were able
to eat so many of those.
It's good, Tama! Delicious!
Yummy in my tummy!
I still can't believe I stuck
with it as long as I did.
It tasted so terrible I almost
passed out a couple of times.
So tell me, why were you
even participating
in a dumpling-eating contest
in the first place?
Garnet's trying to
expand her branding.
Now she's eating competitively!
Stay tuned for more details.
Competitive eating?
Being a multi-faceted celebrity
takes a lot out of you.
So, are these jelly dumplings
world-famous for being so gross?
No, not at all!
They stink now, but they
used to be really delicious!
I like 'em!
[CHARO] I wonder what
could have happened?
It's probably because the
water we use to make them
has gone bad recently.
Whaddaya mean?
[HOST]
It's almost like something
has contaminated the water.
[TAMAZO] I almost forgot.
You were a worthy challenger.
--Let me share this.
--Oh, you really don't have to.
[ACE] You almost beat Tamazo
in an eating contest.
That's impressive!
Well, I was hungry.
And caught up in the moment.
Honestly, no one could be
more surprised than I am!
You can do anything if you
just believe in yourself, Tama!
The power was always inside you!
Right, and thanks again.
I'm stuffed.
Honestly, I was feeling
hungry and kind of down
before you came along.
So, I heard you won the contest!
You rock, Tamazo!
Hey, that intel you gave us
on the temple was no good!
We went up there, wasted our
time, and found nothing!
Have at thee, rakish scoundrel!
Sorry about the goose chase.
Why don't I give you this to
show there are no hard feelings?
It's supposed to
be a treasure map!
--Wow!
--Tama!
[CHARO] Doesn't this
map seem kinda fishy, too?
Don't worry so much!
Would that nice old man
over there give it to me
if it was nothing?
Heh.
So what kind of treasure
does the map lead to?
[DONNY]
Wait for it. It leads...
...to a Dragon Knight!
What the heck's a Dragon Knight?
It's a super-rare monster!
It's a big deal!
Then it's settled. Let's go
and find the Dragon Knight's
Soul Armor and get strong!
[DONNY]
Good luck out there!
Capturing this Dragon Knight
will be extremely difficult.
Lotsa things are difficult,
but they're still
possible, aren't they?
Well, yes, I suppose
you're right.
With the right spirit,
you can do anything!
[BOTH] Believe in yourself,
and bring on the challenges!
[CHARO]
I'll come with you!
Quick question.
Did you have some
kinda plan to obtain
the Dragon Knight's Soul Armor?
[ACE]
Not really.
You didn't come up with
anything on the way here?
I'm sure it'll all work out.
I like how you're
so optimistic, Ace!
[laughs]
It's that positive
point of view you have.
It always makes me feel like
we can accomplish anything.
Even so, I doubt we're going to
find a Soul Armor so easily.
X marks the spot!
Not exactly.
[FLAMIE]
Flame?
--[BOTH gasp]
--[TAMAZO] Tama...?
[ALL]
It's just a dumb Flamie!
[ACE, TAMAZO sigh]
It's all right.
Don't get discouraged;
let's just try and think of
this as a picnic outing.
But I was really looking
forward to getting my hands
on that treasure.
I know, but why did you
want that Soul Armor so badly,
do you think?
Well, If I could
equip the armor.
then it would make me a stronger
Dragon Caller, wouldn't it?
[ACE] If it's possible
to fight like he did...
...I want to be that
strong one day!
Ace...
Tama?
[DEVIL DRAGON grunts]
Huh?!
He's an Ancient Dragon Knight!
[DEVIL DRAGONS growling]
[growling continues]
[ANCIENT DRAGON KNIGHT grunts]
[DEVIL DRAGONS growling]
We've gotta do something!
But how can we help him?
Just stand back!
--Huh?! Uh...
--[TAMA] Tama.
Ouka! Release!
Tamazo's joining in, too!
Cross-On, Tama!
Yah! Awesome.
[ACE gasps]
Let's go, Ace.
Wait, what's going on
with your outfit?
I'll explain later.
Uh, okay.
[OUKA growls]
[DEVIL DRAGON growls]
[OUKA roars]
[DEVIL DRAGONS growling]
Charo!
--[DEVIL DRAGON roars]
--[gasps]
[ACE yelps, grunts]
[CHARO pants]
[ANCIENT DRAGON KNIGHT growls]
[GARNET] I guess you clowns
owe me big time!
[DEVIL DRAGON roars]
[DEVIL DRAGONS growling]
[OUKA barks]
Ah!
[barks]
Tama!
[ANCIENT DRAGON KNIGHT grunts]
[ACE]
Go back.
[ANCIENT DRAGON KNIGHT roars]
[ANCIENT DRAGON KNIGHT snarls]
[ACE gasps] Hurry, you've
gotta turn into an Egg Drop!
[ANCIENT DRAGON KNIGHT groans]
It's too late...
[gasps]
[ANCIENT DRAGON KNIGHT]
But...
...I can still put
my soul to good use...
Whoa. What is it?
I have to ask, what
brought you all the way up
into the mountains, Miss Garnet?
A nice man gave me a map.
So I'm following it!
I wanted to add
Treasure Hunter to my resumé.
So this is all just a PR move.
Time I get back to it.
This treasure isn't going
to find itself, right?
Wait, that map!
Okay, never mind.
[GARNET]
It's just a dumb Flamie!
--I tried to warn her.
--[chuckles]
[BOTH laugh]
What's going on here?
Something happened to make
the water fresh again!
Wow, it is good!
I wonder if all those
monsters were somehow
contaminating the headwaters?
Huh? That would
make me a hero!
And a celebrity hero, at that!
Hey, everyone listen up!
You can all thank me for your
town's water being purified!
[Garnet, dear! Where were you?
We've been following one
bad lead after another
the entire day!
I know, but it all
turned out okay.
We didn't get the Soul Armor,
but I still had fun. And look!
That's neat.
So, Charo, do you have
any idea what this is?
Ohm! It's hard, Tama.
Would you stop chewing
on everything?!
That's a lovely Soul Stone
you have there, Ace.
Hey, Sally.
[CHARO]
A Soul Stone?
It's undeniable proof
that the Ancient Dragon Knight
has accepted you.
You know how an Egg Drop
is the physical body
of a monster, right?
The Soul Stone is tied
to the monster's soul.
Which means monsters
won't share it easily.
[ACE]
A monster's soul?
To obtain one,
you must prove in combat
that you are worthy
of the monster.
Only then will the monster
allow their Soul Stone
to come into your possession.
Follow me, I'll take you
to the Sacred Temple.
[ACE]
So this is the Sacred Temple!
[SALLY] History's greatest
Dragon Callers have come down
this same path to take part in
the Temple's Sacred Ceremony.
I am a priestess.
My duty is to bestow the energy
from the Soul Stone
to a worthy Dragon Caller.
In this way,
new Soul Armor is created
and we fulfill our purpose.
With our source of water
contaminated,
we were no longer able to
carry out our divine duties
here in the Temple.
The Sacred Ceremony explicitly
requires the use of pure water.
I convinced myself that
it was Heaven's will.
And I abandoned all of my
responsibilities as a priestess.
I decided to take
a hard look at my life.
I tried changing my clothes,
I gave cooking a go.
I also tried my luck
on the dating scene,
but it only led
to a broken heart.
Sometimes life can just
be funny that way, you know?
Like when you're ready
to throw in the towel,
and then fate gives you
exactly what you wanted.
[SALLY] All right, Ace,
it's time to come forward.
Have a seat, and then
set the Soul Stone
right there in front of you.
[ACE gasps softly]
[SALLY]
Now stay calm,
and be sure to listen closely
to the Soul Stone's voice.
[gasps]
[ACE gapss]
[VOICE] Forging a strong bond
helps mark the path toward hope.
[ACE]
Goodbye.
[CHARO]
Thanks for everything!
[TAMAZO]
Tama!
[SALLY]
Oh, Ace?
--Uh?
--[CHARO] Hm?
This whole experience
has helped me to reaffirm
the path in life I have chosen.
I've learned that if you
force yourself to do something
that goes against your nature,
it can only lead you
to pain and heartache. Heh.
[GARNET]
Preach it!
Oh? Okay?
There's no point to me
falsifying my public profile!
I'm just going to keep
on being myself
and continue dancing to
the beat of my own drummer!
Good luck to the both of us!
[giggles]
[SALLY]
Yes.
A lot's going on, Tama.
You're right.
[CHARO chuckles]
[TAMAZO giggles]
[ACE]
Thanks for waiting!
It took you long enough!
[ACE chuckles, sighs]
'Kay! Let's make it happen!
You got it, Tama!
Taaa...ma!
Gotcha!
[gasps]
[CHARO]
You're wearing the Soul Armor!
[ACE gasps]
Yeah, yeah, whatever. I'm not
the slightest bit envious.
That armor makes you look
super mega ultra-cool, Ace!
[TAMAZO]
You're a total stud, Tama!
Lookin' extra fine!
[CHARO laughs]
Soul Armor....
[TAMAZO]
Hurray, Tama!
Looks like Ace has
finally Crossed-On!
He's so super cool,
it's giving me goosebumps!
But for some reason,
I've got a bad feeling, Tama.
Next time!
"Mapple Tree", Tama!
Ooh, that sounds kinda tasty!