[ACE] Ms. Herriot, would you
please help me train again?
Yes, please, tama!
Now where's this coming
from all of a sudden?
You're already a Guild
Dragon Caller, kid.
I mostly train people
up to that point.
But you gotta help! I have
to train to become stronger!
Somethin' happen to you?
It was awful!
We got totally creamed
by some evil brat, tama!
So frustrating, tama!
A kid?
That's just sad.
All the more reason
for you to help me!
Hit the gym if you really
wanna get stronger, Ace.
Focus on free weights.
I'm being serious, you know.
Yeah, so am I.
Any Dragon Caller worth his
salt strives to become stronger.
But there are different
ways to achieve that goal.
True strength comes from
figuring out what works for you.
Everybody's gotta find
their own path in this life.
'Cause I have my own path
to walk! That's why.
It's time I headed
out on my own!
Find my own path? But what?
I found my way through
muscle development.
Your way might be
completely different.
[MORGAN]
My sister's being cruelly vague.
But I'd be glad to offer
you a helpful hint, Ace.
If you really want
to be stronger,
learn to listen to the
monsters' voices.
The monsters' voices?
See, now you got the
poor kid all confused!
That's why I was trying not
to get too into the specifics.
Well, excuse me!
[TAMAZO]
Tama...
And just so we're crystal clear,
I'm not talking about
voices like this one.
Huh?
Oh, by the way, Herriot,
Master Dafnes wants us ASAP.
Time for us to head out!
And you're just now telling me?
No, wait, please!
Sorry, kid. It's Guild business.
See ya around.
[TAMAZO crying]
I can't believe the ley line
has become
contaminated so quickly.
I can't force it down!
[roaring]
[DAFNES]
Calamity Immortal Dragon.
It would be disastrous
if he got out.
There's so many, but why?
If it comes down to it, I'll be
forced to use my Reversion.
Oh, yeah!
The cavalry's arrived,
Master Dafnes!
[HERRIOT] That's right,
run back to your nest!
[DAFNES] I appreciate you
two showing up so quickly.
You asked for us,
and we came runnin'!
You shouldn't push
yourself so hard,
trying to settle
things on your own!
You might still look young,
but we know you're not.
How I've missed
the catty back-talk
you girls bring to the table.
All right, let's get to work.
[MORGAN] Looks like
that's all been settled.
[DAFNES]
Though only temporarily.
The ley lines are the arteries
the Drops flow through,
and something's stopping the
energy from traveling further.
[CALAMITY IMMORTAL
DRAGON A roars]
And we can push it back
the next time, too.
That's what we
Dragon Callers do.
Talk about a let-down!
I came just to watch
you fight the dragon.
If you don't take him on, it
will have been a wasted trip.
Who does this annoying
brat think he is, exactly?
Hello, Zeus.
A boy served by a god?
Then that must
make you Star John.
The Master's not as tough
as she's hyped up to be
if she's afraid to
fight that thing!
For a guy who came to watch,
you got an awful
big mouth on ya.
That'll be enough, Herriot.
Yeah, watch what you say.
Old Zeus here
only fights for me.
Well, let's hope you're right.
Huh?
We're leaving.
I'll always hate the Guild.
Those jerks.
If they were so great,
they would've saved my town.
They'll get what's
comin' to 'em.
The monsters' voices.
Ace, he's saying he wants
to fight them, together!
[ACE]
Ouka was my very first monster.
I was so excited
when he came with me.
Then there were the
monsters that trusted me,
and became my allies.
[ACE] Monsters that I battled,
who accepted me as their friend.
[VOICE A] Forging a strong bond
helps mark the path toward hope.
[ACE]
And of course,
the Ancient Dragon Knight
that made me more powerful
by entrusting his soul to me.
Forge strong bonds?
I wanna understand
the monsters better.
To listen to their voices,
and hear what
they're trying to say.
[TAMAZO]
I so hungry, tama.
I wanna eat something that
really sticks to your ribs,
like an egg, tama!
Well, I heard that.
[ACE chuckles]
Let's grab somethin'
to eat. You ready?
[TAMAZO]
Tama?
Tama!
[DAFNES] Not being able to
deal with this on my own
is so frustrating.
[JEST] Are you whining?
That isn't like you.
It's the sad truth,
and as loathe as I may
be to admit the fact,
my power is waning.
You are and always
shall be lovely.
I think I'm beginning
to understand why Vahaton
has high hopes for humans.
Each year, more and more humans
are learning to become
Dragon Callers.
[JEST] But placing too much
of our hope on humans
is running away
from the problem.
I'd also heard that King's
son Ace battled Star John
and was soundly defeated.
[DAFNES]
Yes, this time.
But who can tell what
will happen next time?
The humans are evolving
at an alarming pace, Jest.
Only we, the Dragonoids,
can save the future of
Dragoza and our world.
You know that, don't you?
[DAFNES]
I hope you're right.
[TAMAZO] Okay! Let's do
some training, tama!
Yeah!
Get it together Ace! I'm not
even breaking a sweat, tama!
You can fly!
[TAMAZO]
Tama! Tama! Tama! Tama!
Tama! Tama! Tama!
[TAMAZO yelling]
Down the hatch!
You didn't drink it!
No, that's gross.
You might be deficient
in the guts department
if you give up so easily, tama!
This isn't real
training, anyway.
This is just you goofing
around, instead.
It's better than not
doing anything, tama!
Yeah, whatever.
[phone rings]
What's up, tama?
Charo says he's also hard
at work back in Libria.
I can't wait to see him again
at the Battle Cup, tama!
[phone rings]
Is Charo calling you again?
Bet he's lonely.
"Dear Ace, I know
you're in the market
for a stronger monster
than what you've got,
and I'd like to offer you some
assistance in the matter."
It isn't Charo,
and there's no name.
Seems pretty fishy, tama!
But I received this
message on my D-Gear,
which means a
Dragon Caller sent it.
Someone's pranking you,
tama. Just ignore it.
[TAMAZO]
Here we go anyway, tama!
Ace, you're naïve.
That was totally gross!
That fruit's disgusting.
So yucky, tama!
Fruit that grows where
the Drop flow is stagnant
tastes extra-yucky, tama!
I'll take your word for it.
This place feels eerie, Ace.
Like something terrible is
about to appear, tama-ma!
[ACE] The Drops feel like
they did that one time.
You remember?
When we almost
experienced a Drop Impact
on the outskirts of Libria?
[BOTH gasp]
Ta-Tama?
I told you it was a trap, tama!
Let's get outta here!
No way!
Are you nuts?
We'll just get caught up
in the Drop Impact, tama!
It's a Dragon Caller's
job to try and stop it!
[gasps]
[ACE]
It's like what Torlie said.
The Drop Impacts are proof
that the planet is hurting!
If the source of the
Drops dries out,
then this planet and all
the monsters will die!
That's why we've got
to do something!
If that's the way you feel,
then so be it, tama!
I'll be right here by your side!
Here, Ace! Your Armor
Drop is ready, tama!
Cross-On!
Release!
[yells]
Awesome!
Here they come, Ace!
Right! Go-time!
Light beats out Dark!
Holy Ball!
Yes!
Heck, that was pretty easy!
What the--?
Can you sense it too, Ace?
I can. Something
isn't right here.
[BOTH gasp]
[ACE]
That isn't good. What now?
We're up for a fight if you are!
Good. Let's go!
[TAMAZO]
The Drop disturbance is massive!
Can you handle it, Ace?
I have to.
The Drop flow needs to
return to its natural state.
[gasps]
Good lookin' out!
Thanks for the assist.
Now it's our turn to hit back!
Yeah! Nicely done!
Let's go.
[roars]
He can use his own roar
to power up? Amazing!
We need to strike first!
Then we shall!
It's no good.
I fear we're too late.
Then it's time to
break out Gungnir.
You're right about that!
Follow me, everyone!
I'll combo!
Tama!
Do it!
That's it!
Now give him
everything you've got!
Great work, guys!
Indeed!
This should help to
dissipate the Drop Impact!
What's this?
Is that?
How can there be
so many of them?
This is bad.
[chuckles]
And now what?
Ace, something's coming, tama!
How strange.
That thing... could it be?
[TAMAZO]
Tama!
Tama! So many Dark Drops!
Tama?
The Drop Impact's
dispelled! Incredible.
This power... it's familiar.
[gasps]
It was you!
The Ancient of Dark, tama!
Are you all right?
Wow! You were scary, tama!
How intriguing.
You used your Reversion
to save that human boy.
So be it then. I'll proceed
with my plan alone, if need be.
[DAFNES] I'm sorry you
had to see me like that.
What? No. You don't need
to apologize for saving me.
The only reason I was even here
was to settle the Drop Impact.
No offense, but I didn't
come to save you.
I know, but thank you anyway.
And what brings
you to this place?
It isn't on any
sight-seeing tours.
Um, because--
Someone conned us
into coming out here
to find a mighty monster!
So you walked
right into a set-up.
That's remarkably stupid.
I was just looking for another
way to become stronger.
I warned him not to go, tama!
But would he listen to
Tama? Of course, not!
After watching the way
you fight, Master Dafnes,
I think I know what kinda
strength I'm trying to achieve.
Tama?
Oh?
I wanna get in on
the action too!
To fight, just like
you and Tamazo!
Impossible.
Or at best, improbable.
Human beings lack
the ability to Revert.
What's the big idea, Ace?
Are you trying to steal the
spotlight from me, tama?
[yelps]
I just...
[ACE]
I'll always lag behind.
I don't wanna hold
anyone back anymore.
I'm done with that.
I need to learn
how to see things
from the monsters' perspectives.
Developing stronger
bonds with monsters
is where my path takes me!
Following that path
may not be easy.
I'll need more
training, but I...
...I wanna fight
alongside my monsters.
I see.
Then there's somewhere
that you should visit.
Where's this place I need to go?
Would you please stop
being mysterious
and spit it out, tama?
First, head to the Duen Desert.
Trek across the sands to the
edge where the sun rises,
and you will find a monster
as powerful as a god.
Really?
Do not fear.
That Tamadra will lead you
in the right direction.
Who, Tamazo?
Perhaps you might
succeed on this quest
where many others have failed.
I saw how all of your monsters
were filled with happiness
when fighting together
for your sake.
Although, this chubby one has a
tendency of getting too cocky.
Would you please let go
of my scalp, already?
[SONIA]
When the planet faces a crisis,
the one who embodies the
will of our planet appears,
and the bond between people
and monsters will cross.
Next time.
"Surviving the Storm."
Do you really think you're
ready to face this, Ace?