[NARRATOR]
For untold centuries,
there have been powerful
warriors who fought against
the various crises that
threatened our world.
They harnessed
the power of the monsters
and forged a bond which
eased the planet's anger.
They were the Dragon Callers.
[NARRATOR] Dragon Callers are
born with the special power
to bridge the gap between
the realms of nature,
mankind, and monsters.
When fear and hatred
contaminate the elements
that surround us...
...the Dragon Callers will
rise up with their monsters,
and restore balance
to our world.
The ocean!
That sea breeze feels great!
Hey! A dragon!
Looks to me like a Plesiel!
We've got to be getting close!
[TAMAZO]
Tama?
Wow... awesome!
There, on the horizon!
I see it.
Dragoza!
It would seem
the threads of fate
have brought him right to us.
[JEST] Though whether
or not King's progeny
is worthy of the Tamadora
remains to be seen.
The Ancients have decided
to leave that choice
in the capable hands of Vahaton.
I couldn't capture the Tamadora.
I failed you, Master Jest.
I'm sorry.
Lance, please. There's no need
for you to apologize.
Your failure, too,
was fated in the stars.
Yes...
[CHARO]
Dragoza Island is divided up
into five distinct areas.
Fire, light, wood,
water, and dark.
We're now in the
water-focused town of Crocus.
[ACE] It's way different
from Vienna City.
[TAMAZO] So many different
monsters here, Tama!
Tama, tama, tama tama!
[TAMAZO squeaks]
Ugh. Oh. Oh, hey there!
Tamazo?
[CHARO] Hmm? Don't worry,
that dragon isn't scary.
He's here to give
all the townspeople
rides around the island.
Awesome.
Now let's see here.
Looks like your grandmother's
house should be
just past this street.
[bells chime]
[SONIA] I've confirmed that
the boy and his Tamadora
have arrived on the island.
I'll bring them right away.
[VAHATON]
No need for us to rush.
We've been waiting
for this moment
ever since King's
disappearance, haven't we?
What's a few more hours in
the grand scheme of things?
[knocking at door]
[door clacks open]
Master Vahaton, sir.
[VAHATON]
What is it, Donny?
An Ouka's been spotted, Master.
It's a fire-type monster.
I've heard that it's
living in Rusk forest.
An Ouka?
Don't you worry.
I'll take care of him
before he has a chance
to burn the forest down.
Now, if you please excuse me.
[door clacks open, shuts]
[SONIA sighs softly]
[ACE]
Grandma?
[ANGINE gasps]
I made it.
Is that really you, Ace?
You've grown so much since
the last time I saw you!
[ACE laughs]
Let me introduce everyone!
This is Charo!
It's a real pleasure
to meet you, Mrs. Angine!
[ACE]
And this is Tamazo.
Nice to meet you, Tama!
Huh? Tamazo?
[gasps]
[TAMAZO laughs]
Tama-tama-tama-tama-tama, tama!
I always wanted a Grandma!
[TAMAZO hums]
[ANGINE chuckles]
Oh, my goodness!
[ACE]
Hey, you!
Sorry. He's just
really friendly!
Tama!
I can't remember the last time
I had such a heartfelt greeting.
Well, I've got your
room setup already,
so go on inside,
drop your stuff off
and get a feel of the place.
Thank you very much, ma'am!
[ACE]
Thank you, Grandma!
Ah! Smell that fresh air!
Tama!
[farts]
And you can keep
smelling that fresh air!
[ANGINE] This one used
to be King's room, you know.
[ACE gasps]
Any news on Dad?
Or where he might be?
Nothing.
[ANGINE] So much time has passed
without a word,
or even a simple clue
as to his whereabouts.
We thought he would be here
when your power as
a Dragon Caller awakened.
But I suppose you
can't fight fate.
Here, take this.
One of those?
This particular one
belonged to your father.
It was his D-gear, Ace.
And it should help guide you on
your path to become
a great Dragon Caller,
just like he was.
Do you mean it?
[gasps softly]
Wow! Thank you, Grandma!
[window clatters]
[TAMAZO laughs]
Tama.
But how do I use it?
Tama?
Hands off!
You're going to need
a monster companion
to activate the D-gear,
you won't be able
to operate it without one.
A monster, huh?
Let's find one!
[TAMAZO]
Tama!
Be careful out there, Ace.
It's not as easy as it sounds.
[CHARO] Oh, wow!
That's the real thing!
Can I hold it?
Yeah, why not? I don't know
how to use it anyway.
[CHARO] For starters,
you're going to need to
get a monster Egg Drop
just to get it functional.
What's an Egg Drop?
That's what it's called
when a monster takes
the form of a Drop.
All you have to do is stick
the Drop in your D-gear
and then you can
summon that monster
to fight for you as an ally!
Okay. How do I get an Egg Drop?
[CHARO] Uh... The Dragon
Caller's Guide says
that the monster
has to accept you.
Then it'll turn into an
Egg Drop all on its own.
Okay, you lost me.
Unless I'm mistaken,
it basically means
becoming friends with
the monster in question.
Right on! If I've gotta
have a monster buddy,
I hope it's cool, like a dragon!
No, that's not super likely.
You're just learning, you need
something more entry-level.
Entry-level?
[TAMAZO]
Ace! Ace!
Oh! Like this one?
[CHARO]
That's a Woodsie!
[ACE]
Gotcha!
--[TAMAZO] Tama!
--[CHARO] Ace?
[squeals]
[ACE grunts]
Are you okay?
[TAMAZO]
I know first aid!
[ACE grunts]
Get off...
[TAMAZO]
Ta-Tama, Tamatama. Tama. Tama!
Oh, wow, they're all over!
I guess the Drop Energy
out here is really high.
[CHARO]
Huh?
[ACE]
Hey, come back!
[OUKA squeaks]
[squeals]
[ACE gasps, laughs]
What are you doing?
[OUKA]
Hmm?
I found it.
[hisses]
Wait. What's wrong?
That guy there is
a fire-type monster.
It's called an Ouka,
and the fires it makes
could put this whole
forest in danger.
He doesn't really look
that dangerous to me.
[DONNY] You don't know a thing
about monsters, do you?
You're no Dragon Caller.
[ACE grunts]
[TAMAZO] You could
at least say "Excuse me"!
[DONNY]
I won't let you get away.
[OUKA growls]
[ACE]
Stop that!
[OUKA yelps]
[CHARO]
The Ouka!
[DONNY] You should
mind your own business!
I could've taken care of
the situation by myself.
I didn't mean to hurt him.
--[CHARO] Ace!
--[TAMAZO] Tama!
[ACE gasps]
[TAMAZO]
Ace!
I can't get him to wake up...
[CHARO]
What do we do?!
[SONIA]
Build a fire.
[ACE]
Ah. It's you!
Yes, it's nice to see you again.
Six months ago, word got
out that Oukas lived here.
Unscrupulous Dragon Callers
came to this forest
to seize their power.
Ouka used his fire to
chase them all away.
But now people fear it
as a dangerous monster.
In the end, all the
Oukas were captured.
All except for this one.
I can't believe I hadn't
heard about that...
This guy survived on his own.
That must've been
real tough on him.
I don't really know a
thing about my power.
About what it takes
to be a Dragon Caller.
He's fading into Drop form.
He might disappear!
[ACE gasps softly]
Eat this and get your
strength back, Tama!
I'm sorry...
Please get better, Ouka!
You have to!
[CHARO]
It became an Egg Drop!
That should make it easier for
him to recover his health.
I'm so glad...
[TAMAZO] He must've been
able to sense the kindness
in your heart, Tama!
Is that red D-Gear yours?
Yeah, my grandmother
just gave it to me.
You can take care
of Ouka for now.
When he gets his
strength back, release him.
That little monster's far
too strong for you to handle.
Okay...
How surprising!
I didn't expect you
to bring back an Egg Drop
on your first outing.
And an Ouka at that.
Well, it's only temporary.
Get well soon, little guy.
Rest up, Tama!
I wonder if he'll heal
faster if we warm him up?
Yeah! How about we
wrap him up in a blanket?
[TAMAZO snores softly]
If Dad were still here,
I bet he'd know
exactly what I should do.
[door opens]
[gasps]
I'm sorry... I'm just
so worried about Ouka
that I don't want
to sleep all alone.
[gasps]
[CHARO] We're both boys,
so your Grandma won't mind.
[ACE]
Uh, sure.
Wow. I didn't know he was a boy.
Worcestershire sauce goes great
with sunny-side up eggs...
Quiet.
[ACE] I wonder... Do you
get lonely in the forest?
All by yourself?
[TAMAZO]
Tama!
Tamatama tamatama.
Tama? Tama?
[TAMAZO]
Tama, pushy-push it! Tama!
No? Tama?
And then you... release!
Night Fever, tama!
Tama?
Tama...
Tama, tama!
[HARU] I wonder what Ace
is up to right now?
Like, is he totally hanging out
with Mister Lance on Dragoza?
[phone chimes, vibrates]
[gasps]
Oh, look! A message from Ace!
[HARU]
Huh...?
"I'm doing just fine"?
Is that really all he wrote?
I've been worried
sick about him!
I understand, sweetheart,
but you know Ace
is going to be just fine.
He's a strong one,
just like his mother.
[LENA giggles]
[ANGINE]
What the devil happened in here?
[ACE]
Whoa! Not cool!
Who would do such a thing?
[TAMAZO] Well. I swear
it wasn't me, Tama!
[barks]
Hey, you! You look like
you're feeling way better!
Welcome back, Ouka!
[TAMAZO]
Tama-ma!
[TAMAZO laughs]
Whoa! Wait, I'm not
your dinner, Tama!
Oh, my goodness!
At least the room
was already a mess...
[TAMAZO]
Stop it, Tama! [yelps, laughs]
[OUKA growls]
Don't you dare
even think about it!
That's for our breakfast!
[barks]
Oh, yeah! Nicely done, Ouka!
Guess I won't need to
plug in the toaster.
Ouka wasn't even trying
and look at what the
little guy can do!
[ACE] She said he's
too much for me to handle,
but this isn't so bad.
Right, little guy?
--[OUKA barks]
--[ACE yelps]
What's with all the ruckus?
[GARNET yells]
[growls] So that's why there's
an Ouka in your house.
Kentucky Fried Hairdo! [laughs]
Oh! Sorry about that. Though
he's not really my monster.
Well, of course he isn't!
A total amateur like you
could never handle an Ouka!
[ACE]
Anyway, what brings you here?
Master Vahaton sent me
here this morning.
He said he wants me to escort
you guys over to him.
The Master Vahaton,
the protector and backbone
of the township of Crocus?
Meeting with him is
beyond a big deal!
The Master's an
old friend of mine.
I let him know that
you were coming.
He's ready to teach you
a little about the importance
of a Dragon Caller's spirit.
Go on and meet him.
Oh. Okay.
But before we go to him,
we need to return this
little guy to the forest.
[OUKA groans]
[ACE] I guess this place
is as good as any.
[OUKA yelps, squeaks]
Goodbye. Take care
of yourself, Ouka!
Bye-bye, Tama!
[OUKA]
Hmm...?
Let's go...
[CHARO]
Yeah.
[squeaks]
[howls]
Poor guy's calling out
for his friends.
He'll keep howling,
waiting for the other Oukas
to return to the forest.
Stop it, pipsqueak.
There's nothing we can do for
him, so let's just keep going.
[OUKA howls]
[ACE whimpers]
[CHARO]
Huh? Hey, wait!
Oh, come on.
[pants]
Hey, listen to me.
It's not just dangerous to stay
out here all by yourself,
it's also lonely.
I know I'm... I'm not a
Dragon Caller yet, or anything.
They say I can't handle you.
I'm sorry. "Handle you,"
you have a choice.
Would you lend me your power?
We'd make a great team.
[OUKA growls]
So, no?
Would you stop
prattling on and on?!
Ask him nicely, and then
say the stinking magic word!
Have you considered
kneeling down before him?
Pin the shoulders, Tama!
[ACE] Would you all stop
teasing and let me think?!
I actually was serious.
[DONNY]
Pest control, comin' through!
Not you guys again!
Not you again, back at ya!
You again, again, Tama!
Ouka's a dangerous monster--
it's time you realized that.
And there's no way
you can control him!
That's not true!
Ouka isn't a dangerous monster,
he's actually really nice!
Move aside!
I'm gonna defeat this Ouka.
Then his Egg Drop will be mine!
And I'll earn the
respect of the guild.
[yells]
Release!
Ace, this is bad!
[ACE growls]
I won't let you
threaten these woods!
Go, Aqua Fighter!
[WOODSIES screaming]
Whoa! What's going on?
[CHARO]
That was a Woodsie nest!
[TAMAZO]
This is no good, Tama!
You blundering doofus!
Watch your aim next time!
[DONNY grunts]
Stop!
[OUKA panting]
[WOODSIES squeaking]
[OUKA growls]
[gasps]
You should try using
Ouka's power.
[ACE]
What?
Ace, he's saying he wants
to fight them--together!
[gasps]
[OUKA barks]
Let's do this, Ouka!
[ACE]
Now! Lend me your power!
[yells]
Release!
[OUKA squeals]
[WOODSIES screaming]
[WOODSIES squealing]
[TAMAZO]
Now's your chance, Tama!
[CHARO] He's right, Ace!
Shout "Inferno Blast!"
Inferno Blast!
[OUKA roars]
[WOODSIES screaming]
Well done, Tama!
Nice job! You got 'em, Ace!
That was awesome!
[gasps]
[barks]
Couldn't have done it
without Ouka.
[growls]
[DONNY sighs]
[VAHATON] Getting Ouka
to join you as an ally
was splendid on
your part, my boy!
[ACE]
Huh? Who's that?
[GARNET] The Ancient of Water--
Master Vahaton.
Purity antler guy?
[VAHATON] You sure do remind me
a great deal of King, you know?
And that Tamadora certainly
brings back memories.
My Tamadora?
It's a species of monster
that was quite prevalent
in ages past.
But it's been far
too long since any
were spotted out in the wild.
Then does that mean
you're, like, super rare?
Tamazo is special!
[VAHATON]
You fought with such bravery
to protect your friend, Ace.
Tamazo and Ouka could see
you had an open heart,
which made them willing
to give you a hand.
[thunk]
[VAHATON] The true purpose
of a Dragon Caller
lies not in fighting monsters
that appear among us.
Our world is full of Drops, and
therein lies our sacred duty.
It falls to the Dragon Caller
to maintain balance
between the elements,
creating order amidst the chaos.
King loved peace and gave
his all to save the world.
And to keep you safe, too.
[gasps]
[VAHATON]
That D-Gear you have there.
King left that because
he knew you'd need it.
Even now he's looking out
for his boy, it would seem.
[OUKA squeaks]
[ACE]
Dad...
[VAHATON laughs]
Well, it seems like Ouka here
is rather fond of you!
And now it's my turn
to welcome you
to Dragoza Island, my dear boy.
If you'd like to stay here
and train in Crocus,
we'll do everything we can
to help you make
the most of your unique talents.
Okay!
You're practically
a Dragon Caller!
Tama, ta!
I never would've done it
without you, Charo!
[CHARO giggles]
Heh.
[laughs]
[OUKA squeaks]
[ACE]
Hi, Ouka, my name's Ace.
So! We can get to know each
other better while I study.
Sound good?
I never thought that
Ouka would save me.
Sorry... I guess...
[ACE chuckles]
[TAMAZO] But... we still
don't know who you are!
[TAMAZO] Ace is well on his way
to becoming a Dragon Caller.
But it's not all smooth sailing!
There is something Ace
is still missing, Tama.
Wanna know what it is?
I'm not telling, Tama!
Next ep!
"Soul Armor," Tama!
[gasps]
I accidentally told you!