[NARRATOR]
The Battle Cup,
where ambitious young Dragon
Callers come to compete against
one another and determine
who's the best of the best.
It's a high-stakes tournament
where matches are fought
based on fighter classes.
They're all competing
for the glory,
as well as the Golden Egg.
The late Ancient of Light,
Master Lukes, banned Soul Brave,
an ancient Dragon
Caller technique.
However, that ban was lifted
by the current Ancient
of Light, Master Jest.
Utilizing their Soul Armor
and various monsters,
these Dragon Callers are aiming
to bring home the big win!
Ready yourselves, challengers,
for the moment of truth!
Use Valkirie's Soul!
It's time, you guys!
[BOTH groan]
Way to go, Garnet!
That's what's up. You pulled
a ton of Light Drops!
Garnet's really good
at this, tama!
Even non-attack
skills are useful,
the Dragon Caller just has
to know when to use them.
Garnet swings back at him,
but Starjohn is still standing!
Truly spectacular!
We are witnessing
a high-level battle worthy
of the finals round!
[CROWD cheers]
Nice job withstanding
what I like to call
the "Girl-Monsters'
Skill Festival"!
Well, you won't be so
lucky next time around!
If you use it again,
I'll be ready.
I am done playing with you!
You're the one that's over!
Now, Naga!
Menace, Activate!
[STARJOHN grunting]
[METAL]
There it is, Naga's Menace!
The same skill that
lead to Klein's defeat
in the semi-finals!
Zeus is stuck like
a deer in headlights!
And young Starjohn
is rooted to the spot!
Not being able to do anything
must be humiliating.
You realize, you're only
delaying the inevitable.
While you're on hold,
let's have Cupid use her healing
skill to get the ball rolling.
[METAL]
And now Garnet's showing off!
She heals herself with panache,
as a paralyzed Starjohn
stands waiting!
Uh. You're toast.
Okay guys! Are you ready?!
[MAN 32A]
All right!
It's finally time to finish
this rude little kid off!
Now, beat that punk up!
[CROWD]
Garnet! Garnet!
Angelion, and Mermaid!
Use Guard Stance!
[METAL] She just turned the Dark
and Fire Drops into Heart Drops!
[grunts]
[GARNET]
I still haven't fully recovered.
Should I use these
Drops to heal myself?
Or something else?
I always push forward,
all the way!
Time for Attack Stance!
Okay, let's go Valkyrie!
[METAL]
Attack Stance, Light!
The Coliseum is now filled
with Light Drops!
[CROWD cheers]
How long are you
gonna drag this out?
Sorry for the wait!
Let me send a few Valkyrie
Soul combos your way!
That's that!
[CROWD cheers]
[FAN 29A]
Yeah, Garnet!
Master, you're so cool!
This fight isn't over.
Tama?
[METAL]
Starjohn withstood the attack!
[gasps]
[laughs] After all of
your talk, that was it?
Hilarious. You really
crack me up.
[screams]
--Oh, no!
--No way!
He blasted her!
That's gotta hurt, tama!
[METAL] Is Garnet going
to throw in the towel?
I won't give up... Ever!
That looked painful.
It's getting hard to watch.
Shouldn't we stop the
match, Master Jest?
A fight can only end when
one of the combatants
is knocked unconscious,
or willingly surrenders.
Those are the rules
of the Battle Cup.
Master Lukes would've
stopped this.
My predecessor isn't in charge.
The Battle Cup is a place
for honest competition,
for young Callers to
train and to grow,
a place to hone one's skills.
This ideal tournament was
what the late Master Lukes
had always envisioned.
That's correct.
[screams]
[ELDORA] There's no training or
growth potential in her torment.
[JEST] This year,
several young Dragon Callers
have shown rather astonishing
growth, in my opinion.
Ace and Garnet specifically,
both were able to use
Soul Brave due to the
pressure they faced.
And that's the real point,
the strongest Dragon Callers
rise to meet the challenge.
[screams]
Her goose is cooked, tama!
Garnet's one of the toughest
Dragon Callers I know,
but her outlook is pretty grim.
[CROWD murmurs]
Please be okay.
You're stubborn, aren't ya?
Just call it quits,
you're finished.
[GARNET grunts]
Over my dead body, tough guy!
Yeah? Fine!
Heh, heh.
[screams]
Starjohn lands a solid hit, and
it knocks Garnet to the ground!
She's hurt!
We should help her,
whaddaya say, guys?
Let's crash this match, tama!
Uh. Uh, wha...?!
[GARNET whimpers]
Master, please stay down!
It's not worth it!
Just stay down!
Come on, Garnet! Go for the top!
[MAN 32A]
You can do it!
[MAN 32B]
We love you, Garnet!
Go, Garnet!
You must be real weak.
If that attack knocked you down,
how can you ever
hope to beat me?
[CROWD]
Garnet! Garnet!
Garnet! Garnet! Garnet!
[GARNET whimpering]
Huh, I guess you're done.
[GARNET]
Hold it.
[STARJOHN gasps]
[yells]
[CROWD cheers]
Oh, wow! She's amazing!
You sure are persistent.
'Kay, Zeus, finish her off.
Zeus?
Yo!
The fight is over.
Nothing to finish.
[CROWD murmurs]
Did she just faint,
while standing up?
[exhales]
What's going on with her?
That's the end!
Garnet can no longer
continue the battle!
Not so fast! I haven't
finished showing off
all my moves to my
new sparring partner!
That's enough!
Uh?
Hey, you! Isn't this guy
breaking the rules?
He can't just jump
in here, can he?
The match was already over.
However, attacking
your opponent
after the match is
prohibited behavior.
It's Prohibited, tama!
[STARJOHN]
Attacking her?
You're mistaken.
I wouldn't dream of doing
something like that.
[METAL] The winner of the Class
B Finals is Starjohn!
[CROWD]
Garnet! Garnet!
The crowd is going crazy for
the bravery Garnet showed
in that last battle!
What are you looking at, loser?
I'm ganna take you down,
for Garnet's sake!
[laughs] You say that
with a straight face,
but we both know, I've
beaten you before!
Now that's what I call a battle!
Garnet fought like
a little lioness!
Right, Morgan?
Uh? Morgan?
Morgan?
[GARNET whimpers]
Okay. That should
just about do it.
Are you okay?
No. I'm far from okay.
I was dead on arrival.
[TIGER]
Huh?
[TAMAZO]
Tama?
That goofy expression was
broadcast across the world!
That face killed my
career as an idol!
Oh, that.
Now, now, at least you
have your health!
That's a relief, isn't it Ace?
Oh, yeah!
You realize, it's nearly time
for the next battle to begin.
Huh?! Well, then I've gotta go!
If you win this next round,
you'll be the Class C champion!
Go for it!
[ACE]
Mm-hm.
Good luck in the final.
I'm sorry we won't get
our chance to battle.
Oh. Thanks.
Take care of yourself, now.
[TAMAZO]
Tama.
I'll wipe the floor with
that jerk! I swear it!
Let's do it, tama!
[KROELL chuckles]
Tama?!
Tama?
[KROELL chuckles]
I'm afraid that's going
to be impossible.
What?
[KROELL] Before you have the
opportunity to face off against
Starjohn, you'll have to
win the finals of Class C.
However, I don't plan
to just let that happen.
And you are...?
My name is Kroell, boy,
and I'm not afraid
to get my hands dirty,
if it means winning.
[KROELL laughs]
That guy...
...didn't wash his hands, tama.
[DAFNES] Starjohn Junior.
Do you have a minute?
[STARJOHN] Oh, you're
that old lady from before.
I'm not an old lady.
I'm an Ancient!
I knew your father, he was
a capable Dragon Caller.
The sort of man that was
up for any challenge,
and was well respected for
his sense of fairness.
I have better things to
do than get lectured.
I was reminiscing about
Starjohn Senior.
Thinking about what he would
say if he could see you now.
What do you think?
[STARJOHN] You have no right
to talk about that!
Well he's touchy.
I wonder why all
Light-attributed men
have to be so difficult.
[TORLIE] I've never seen
the crowd get so excited
during the matches.
It's because of the SDF's
Drop display technology!
I'd like to thank you
for all your assistance!
I half-expected the
Ancients of the Guild
to roundly reject our
offer of help.
I'll come out and say it.
I was afraid you'd believe
the ability to see Drops
was a privilege reserved
for Dragon Callers.
I personally think this
is an awesome device!
I want everyone to see the
dangers related to the Drops,
and this will help more people
understand how Drops work!
I believe that this is the first
step to a better tomorrow.
Which is precisely what
we believe, Master Torlie.
[NYUDO] Competent, energetic,
though far too ideological.
He's a fine young man.
But, he's also quite naive.
With this tech, the
people will gain power
equal to the Dragonoids and
they'll have the SDF to thank.
[gasps]
Hey, Morgan!
I finally found you!
I wasn't hiding.
Who was that?
You got a new friend?
None of your business.
Come on, who was it?
Just tell me!
What are you doing
all the way out here?
Oh, right!
I was so proud of Garnet,
she saw that battle through
all the way to the end!
Ugh. Such a horrible spectacle.
Oh yeah, that Starjohn kid did
take things a little too far.
No, not him!
I was talking about Garnet!
That fight was so pathetic,
I couldn't even watch it!
She got beaten to a pulp!
Huh?
It's her own fault if
she got herself hurt.
All of those weaklings
should just give up.
What's going on
with you, Morgan?
I see things clearly now.
Only the strong
should be allowed
to become Dragon Callers.
So, what?
You're siding with
that little weasel
who thinks strength
is all that matters?
Oh, my sweet sister.
Life must be nice and simple
for somebody as soft in
the head as you are.
Are you trying to pick
a fight with me?
You want to? Is that it?
You can't actually be serious.
Oh! Of course,
I'm totally kidding.
You never could take a
joke, Herriot. [laughs]
What's gotten into her?
Man, I hope she didn't start
going out with some weirdo.
[JEST] By lifting
the ban on Soul Brave,
the world as we know
it will change.
Everyone has now
witnessed the power
of this age-old technique
for themselves.
No matter how much of a
fuss the Ancients make,
they can't hope to
change this flow.
I'm glad the ban is done.
I've always been pro-Soul Brave.
[laughs] And yet, you've never
once used it in real combat.
That's because all of my
opponents were unworthy.
But everything has changed now.
Lance won't need it.
Sorry, Devi. Would you
give us some room?
Uh?!
[yelps]
[HERRIOT, DEVI sigh]
--Huh?
--Devi?
Hey, you're Lance's
monster, Devi.
C'mere, I just wanna
squeeze you forever!
Look but don't touch, devi.
[sighs]
You seem kinda down
in the dumps, devi.
So where's your boss, Lance?
You're always with
him, aren't you?
What about you?!
Don't I usually see you
with your twin, devi?
[BOTH sigh]
If you need someone
to talk to, I'm here.
That's supposed to
be my line, devi.
I've had a plethora
of life experiences!
Yeah, right.
Like I'd spill my problems
to a stress ball.
Devi?
[screaming]
Stop it.
[gasps] No! Stay away!
[screams]
[whimpers]
[yells]
You should just
do that next time!
Yeah, I guess so.
But isn't that kinda mean?
That kind of
wishy-washy attitude
is the reason the monsters
keep disrespecting you!
It'll work out anyway, because
you'll always be there for me.
Oh, boy.
[JEST]
Master Lukes!
Yes? What's the matter, Jest?
Something awful
happened to Starjohn.
He was wounded during a battle.
He's desperately in need
of your help, Master Lukes.
[LUKES grunting]
[sighs] That should
take care of it,
but you've pushed yourself
too hard, Starjohn.
I know, Master.
This time, I couldn't afford to
lose, or to back down at all.
The pride of our tribe
was at stake.
What good is pride to
the tribe if one of their
greatest warriors is
consumed by Soul Brave?
As ever, you speak truly.
This is proof that Soul
Brave is dangerous.
From now on, I intend to
ban its use in the Guild.
But Master, if you ban the use
of Soul Brave within the Guild,
you'll limit the powers
of future generations
of Dragon Callers!
But power isn't everything,
even for a Dragon Caller.
[STARJOHN'S DAD]
I understand.
It's been nice
knowing you, Jest.
Say goodbye to King for me!
So what do you plan to do now?
Develop a new strategy.
I'll work out one that's much
safer to use than Soul Brave.
I see.
I look forward to your success.
[BOTH]
Bye, Starjohn!
Ancient Lukes! I brought
these flowers in for you!
Thank you very much, Morgan.
[HERRIOT]
And this is from me!
Oh, yeah?
I wonder what it could be!
[laughs]
[BOTH gasp]
[BOTH laughing]
So, my friends.
I've been thinking about
relinquishing my title
to my disciple.
So then pick me, Master!
I wanna be the next Ancient!
Yeah, Sis would be
a great Ancient!
[laughs] Well, you're still a
little too young, dear child.
But she's gonna grow
up in no time, right?
[HERRIOT]
Mm-hm!
Not long after that,
Master Lukes passed away and
our lives completely changed.
Morgan and I had
always been together.
But suddenly, we were separated.
I was reunited with my sister
after graduating
from the Academy.
I saw her for the first time in
years at the Guild Exam site.
[gasps] Morgan.
Is that really you?
Long time no see, Sister!
Wow, Morgan!
It's hard to believe
how grown up you look!
It's been so long!
And I became a Dragon
Caller just like you!
Now, wherever they send
you, I can come too!
I can fight right beside you!
Oh, yeah!
[BOTH sigh]
She used to be such an
adorable little girl.
Stop squeezin' me!
[HARU]
Ace!
[ACE]
Uh.
Hey, Haru!
I can't believe you made
it to the finals!
Just don't push
yourself too hard.
I won't, but I can't afford
to get knocked out.
I get it.
Best of luck in your next match!
Thanks!
Gee, Ace. You're
such a cool guy!
Wha...?
He's the second coolest guy
around here. After me, that is.
Yeah?! I don't think I could
handle Ace being any cooler!
[laughs]
I gotta go.
Good luck out there!
I'm cheering for you
with all my heart!
--Thank you!
--Tama!
[TAMAZO] Everybody's
pretty worried, tama.
Especially after watching what
happened in Garnet's battle.
Hey Ace, are you scared
at all, tama?
You could really
get hurt, you know.
Yeah. What's new?
Lukes was misguided.
[LUKES]
But power isn't everything,
even for a Dragon Caller.
You can't hope to achieve
anything that will last
without power to back it.
[METAL]
All right!
The finals for Class C
are about to begin!
It'll be a guaranteed must-see!
[JEST]
So, dawns a new era
for a stronger breed
of Dragon Callers.
Okay! Let's win this!
Tama!
Time to show the world
what I'm made of.
I'll start by taking you down.
[ACE] We've finally reached
the Class C finals.
Tamazo, everyone,
we have to win this!
But as it turns out,
my opponent, Kroell,
is a seriously
dangerous guy.
Next time: "Appalling!
Kroell's Whip."
The way he fights is
totally unforgivable!