[NARRATOR]
The Battle Cup,
where ambitious young Dragon
Callers come to compete against
one another and determine
who's the best of the best.
It's a high-stakes tournament
where matches are fought
based on fighter classes.
They're all competing
for the glory,
as well as the Golden Egg.
The late Ancient of Light,
Master Lukes, banned Soul Brave,
an ancient Dragon
Caller technique.
However, that ban was lifted
by the current Ancient
of Light, Master Jest.
Utilizing their Soul Armor
and various monsters,
these Dragon Callers are aiming
to bring home the big win!
Ready yourselves, challengers,
for the moment of truth!
[METAL] This year's Battle Cup
has been an intense competition.
Lance is the Class A champion.
In Class B, Starjohn,
and after rising
through the ranks,
Ace is the champion of Class C!
And now, Ace and
Starjohn will square off
the winner will be Lance's
opponent in the last battle.
Who will become the
strongest Dragon Caller?
Lance?
Starjohn? Or could it be Ace?
[CROWD cheers]
[METAL] Ladies and gentlemen,
your attention, please.
The penultimate match of the
tournament will begin shortly.
You only have a few minutes
to return to your seats.
[TORLIE] Ace's power
has grown exponentially
and more rapidly than
I'd ever imagined.
He turned things
around on Kroell,
he might even have as
much skill as luck.
Oh. Yes.
He might at that,
maybe he'll even win!
[ELDORA]
But Starjohn is in Class B,
an entire rank ahead of Ace,
so it will be quite a challenge.
[JEST]
I suppose anything's possible.
In any case, it will be
an interesting battle.
The real battle's
about to start.
I refuse to let him win.
Just don't give up, and always
remember to go for the top!
Our objective is to pulverize
that obnoxious brat, tama!
You're so much stronger
than you were.
I know you've got what
it takes to defeat him!
Yeah.
[STARJOHN panting]
[laughs]
[panting]
[STARJOHN]
The way you fight.
I think it's really cool!
You must've trained really
hard to get to where you are.
So awesome!
I wish I could become a cool
Dragon Caller like you!
[yelps]
My name is Zeus.
I am a god.
There we go!
[gasping]
Prepare yourself for
the Wrath of God!
[GARNET screams]
Thanks, Zeus-y!
But what took ya so long?
[screams]
You're stubborn, aren't ya?
Just call it quits,
you're finished.
[GARNET groaning]
Over my dead body,
tough guy!
Yeah? Fine.
Heh, heh.
[screams]
[ACE]
I won't let him off easily.
It's payback time.
[GARNET] You can't afford
to underestimate him
just because you've
gotten stronger.
[CHARO]
Garnet?
[GARNET]
Starjohn's strength is palpable.
He can't be overcome
with willpower
or fighting spirit alone.
He'll back you into a corner.
How will you react when he does?
That's the key to victory.
Garnet's actually dishing
out good advice, tama.
That's strange.
She doesn't seem like herself.
I know.
Maybe she took too many
blows to the head?
[GARNET grunts]
[BOTH whimper]
[gasps]
[GARNET] You better put up
a decent fight out there.
I'll be watching.
I'll even half-heartedly
wish you "good luck."
Of course, I don't
expect you to win.
[ACE] This must be so
frustrating for her.
And still, she gave you
that little pep-talk.
You'll have to fight
for Garnet, Ace,
and for the rest of
us who are out.
For our friends!
Let's win this, tama!
[ACE]
Mm-hm.
Looks like I'll have quite
a crowd for the next fight.
It won't be long.
Eh? [laughs]
Congratulations on securing
the Class A title.
[DEVI]
Devi?
But I wouldn't get too
used to being called
champion if I were you,
'cause you still have
to get through me!
Who do you think you're
talking to, devi?!
Mind your tongue!
When I beat your master,
you're free to come with me.
I've already started
making room for you.
What did you say, ya twerp?!
Don't take Ace too lightly.
[STARJOHN]
Huh?
You'll have to beat Ace to get
to me and he's grown stronger.
[laughs] Well, okay.
Thanks for the heads up.
But, I'm not really that worried
about squaring off with him.
I'm gonna wipe the floor
with that wannabe.
Devi's totally gonna
wipe the floor with you,
ya annoying little so-and-so--!
Idiot.
[CROWD cheers]
Here!
Oh, thanks a lot!
You're too kind. Thank you!
This battle is really
important for Ace.
We need to have energy
to cheer him on!
[MAN 35A]
Yeah! Ace is going to need
our support to take that
nasty little bully down
The kid fights dirty!
[WOMAN 35A]
You said it!
That brat is in dire
need of a whoopin'!
Thanks for the snack, Haru.
Yes dear, so thoughtful!
[METAL]
We apologize for the wait,
but here come the
Dragon Callers now!
[CROWD cheers]
So it begins.
It's time. Good luck!
[METAL] The fight we've
all been waiting for.
As the champions of Class B
and Class C go head to head,
striving for supremacy!
Just look at that face.
That's the look of a
determined young man
out to accomplish
something great.
[METAL] This Representative
Battle between Ace and Starjohn
may go down as one of the most
hotly contested matches
of the tournament!
[CROWD cheers]
[ACE]
Cross-On!
Cross-On, tama! Hi-yah! Ha!
Oh! Awesome!
Release!
Okay, guys! Release!
[WHITE DRAGON roars]
[DARK DRAGON KNIGHT roars]
[LEVIATHAN roars]
[CROWD cheers]
He released his monsters?
Does that mean he isn't
gonna use Soul Brave?
Ouka!
Go, White Dragon! Leviathan!
Nefer, and Verche!
[METAL] Ace was able to make
the first strike, however,
all of his attacks were avoided
or blocked by Starjohn!
Now that was just adorable.
It's like you really
think a Class C loser
stands a chance against
someone like me.
That's right. I've gotten
stronger since last time.
And I'm going to stop you here!
[yells]
Tamazo! Dark Dragon Knight!
Let's go!
[DARK DRAGON KNIGHT roars]
[TAMAZO yells]
[yells]
Ouka! Blast him!
[STARJOHN screams]
[ZEUS]
Huh?
[METAL]
That one was a clean hit!
Ouka's attack makes it through
Starjohn's defenses!
[CROWD cheers]
[BOTH laugh]
Way to go out there!
Now, keep it up!
He had his heart set on letting
his monsters hit first,
so he waited to use Soul Brave.
But from here on out,
it's different.
All right! Come back!
[TAMAZO]
Yeah!
Horus! Soul Brave.
There it is!
Ace's Soul Brave is active!
[ACE yells]
[METAL]
Uh-oh, swing and a miss!
What?
[LENA, HARU gasp]
[ANGENE]
Uh!
No, Ace.
I'm afraid it won't
be that easy.
Huh. So now you've
activated your Soul Brave.
Good work.
Really. I'm impressed.
[STARJOHN]
But you're still just a Class C.
You can't hope to defeat me,
even with Soul Brave.
You knocked me down
in front of this crowd,
you're gonna pay for
that humiliation.
Wrath of God.
[screams]
[METAL] Zeus lands his
Wrath of God attack!
That's gotta hurt!
Ace!
Come on!
I knew it.
Backed into a corner.
[gasps] Oh, my Drops.
Don't even think about it!
Go Verche! Nefer!
[ACE groans]
[HARU gasps]
[METAL] Starjohn's leader
skill multiplies Nefer
and Verche's attack power
to be eight times higher!
Didn't you say you'd
changed since I beat you?
'Cause you're still
pretty weak in my opinion.
I expected you to put up a
better fight than this, though.
But then, you are a Class C.
No. I'd say you're a D...
E... F...
Class G or H. Who knows?
Maybe they'll start
a Class Z for ya!
[exhales] Cute.
I'm not going to waste
Zeus's attack on you.
Nefer!
Verche!
[METAL]
Ace is under assault again!
[ALL gasping]
[METAL] And he doesn't have
access to his monsters!
[VERCHE roars]
[METAL] He's really got his back
against the wall this time!
[panting]
[ACE] No, am I going to
lose to him, again?
[TAMAZO]
Never give up!
[gasps]
Tamazo!
[TAMAZO]
Ace, we're still here for you!
Believe in us!
Believe in yourself!
In myself...?
[STARJOHN laughs]
Game over.
Don't underestimate us!
[yells]
[STARJOHN groans]
A last minute save!
What a beautiful counterstrike
coming from Ace!
All right!
The monsters reached
out to help him!
It's like their hearts are
joined as one fighting force!
His monsters made that
attack independently,
because their master
needed their help.
That's Ace's true power.
Wow, not bad, Ace.
No way!
[groans] Nefer, Verche, what
were you worthless idiots doing,
letting him get the drop
on us like that?!
Hurry up and come back here now!
That boy is the absolute worst.
Why is he so rude?
Starjohn doesn't
have a connection
to his monsters like Ace does.
[LENA, HARU]
Uh?
And not just the monsters.
That child has no one.
[ACE gasps]
[METAL] Ace's Soul Brave
is active again!
[ACE yelling]
[ZEUS groans]
[STARJOHN screams]
It looks like Ace still
has plenty of fight!
[STARJOHN] How could you
wimps let this happen?!
I expected more
from you dummies!
Why don't you start
fighting better, huh?!
Hey, now!
Don't go takin' your mistakes
out on your own team!
He's right! That's just ugly!
[MAN 35B]
Hey, hotshot!
Why don't you take care
of your monster's health?
[STARJOHN]
Huh? What's that?
Hold on.
Why are all of those people
sitting in the
audience booing me?
Oh, I get it! I need to recover
my monster's health!
Easy enough.
Time for Holy String!
[gasps]
[STARJOHN]
Get him!
What's wrong with you, Zeus?
Get the lead out, would ya?
Something's up with Zeus.
He's moving strangely.
I wonder if the Heart
Drops he pulled
weren't enough to heal him?
[ZEUS growls]
[ACE] He didn't receive the
healing benefits of Holy String?
Of course! I've got it!
[ACE]
You guys aren't a real team!
You've just been fighting
individually this whole time!
[gasps]
[METAL]
Unbelievable!
A shocking factoid has been
revealed at a critical moment!
Apparently, Starjohn didn't
release Zeus at all!
What?! Really?
[ELDORA] It looks like
Ace figured it out.
[DAFNES]
Yes, Starjohn's Achilles Heel.
[JEST sighs]
Go Ace! Go Ace!
[CROWD]
Go Ace! Go Ace! Go Ace! Go Ace!
Thank you.
I can't accept
the way you fight,
that's why I have to beat you!
Right now!
Quiet, quiet, quiet!
Whatever! I don't need
you guys anyway!
I'll take him down
all by myself!
[JEST]
This battle is over.
[LANCE]
Let's go, Devi.
[DEVI]
Okie dokie, devi!
[squawks]
[ACE]
God Burning...
...Attack!
[screams]
[VERCHE groans]
[ZEUS groans]
[STARJOHN whimpers]
[laughs nervously]
Okay, so now it's
my turn, right?
Zeus.
Hey, Zeus!
Get him!
[ZEUS]
I can't.
We are defeated.
What?! Uh?
What do you think you're doing?!
Get up and give him
the Wrath of God, already!
[ZEUS grunts]
Young warrior,
the victory is yours.
A concession. Ace wins!
Master Jest, the
Ancient of Light,
has just called the fight!
Congratulate our victor.
The Class C champion, Ace!
[CROWD cheering]
Lena! Ace did it!
I never imagined my boy
would make it this far!
Indeed.
He keeps surprising us,
doesn't he?
I feel I deserve a
little credit for his win.
[CHARO]
Ace!
[TIGER]
That was a great battle!
You just put on a total
butt-kicking clinic, my man!
Just watching it got
me all fired up!
I heard you guys cheering
for me when I was struggling.
It gave me strength.
[ALL gasp]
We did it!
Did you see that, tama?
Want some more, tama?!
Starjohn...
This is your fault!
We lost the match,
and it's all your fault!
[ZEUS grunts]
[STARJOHN]
Did ya hear me?!
I said it's all your fault!
[TAMAZO] Looks like he didn't
change the slightest bit, tama.
Guess not.
[VAHATON] It seems like
our young Ace has a knack
for forging connections
with everyone.
[TORLIE] Person to person,
person to monster,
and maybe even human
to Dragonoid.
[VAHATON] Abilities like
his have the power
to change the world,
for the better, hopefully.
[TORLIE]
Yes.
The outcome is as expected.
[JEST]
The Ancients are all too naive.
One day, Dragoza Island will
have to face grave danger.
I wish to prevent that.
That's the truth.
I lifted the ban on Soul Brave
during this Battle Cup
for that very reason.
I will save Dragoza
Island from danger.
And I'll show the
Ancients my power.
The power to protect our home,
to keep it safe.
By defeating him.
At last, it's the final battle.
[ACE] It's almost time for
my match against Lance.
He's been cocky since
the first day we met.
And I was never able
to get ahead.
But maybe now...
Next time: "Battle!
Ace Versus Lance."
Lance, let's do this!