Who're you?
[MORGAN giggles, laughs]
Recognize me? It's Morgan:
the younger and prettier half
of the Dragon Caller Twins!
Ms. Morgan?
You made it all the way to the
final room of the exam, Ace.
Good job!
He just got lucky!
You'll now enter the
last phase of your test.
And the rules are quite simple.
This is a one-on-one,
live-or-die battle against
the beautiful but deadly
Guild Dragon Caller, Morgan!
Deadly?
For real?
[giggles]
She's just laughing at us.
She's so much stronger!
There's just no way
that Ace could beat her!
I can't believe
what I'm hearing!
[BOTH gasp]
You guys seem to be
missing the real point here.
A Guild Dragon Caller's
sacred duty is to dissipate
the Drop Impacts that
threaten our very world,
or to die trying.
That's the point of this
whole examination--
to see if you're good enough
to rise to that responsibility!
[CHARO whimpers] Don't worry.
This is all just a test, right?
It's not like it can
really be life or death--
[gunshot]
Phoo. Maybe now you can see
the severity of your situation?
[growls]
[MORGAN giggles]
For the big finale,
I brought my
extra-special Studmon.
Be a dear, and give me
all you got, okay?
What's a Studmon?
Short for Stud-Monster.
Sounds more marketable that way.
Yeah, well, we have an entire
team of Studmons on our side!
So, think you can
win this, Ace?
Uh-huh! I just have
to defeat her.
Then I'll become a
Guild Dragon Caller!
It's time to get this
show on the road!
Ready... Fight!
--[laughs]
--[bell clangs]
From the depths
of the darkness...
...tear through the light
and come to my side.
Grant me your strength
that I might defeat my enemies.
And let me prove to you that
even beauty has its dark side.
[giggles]
Release!
[VAMPIRE LORD growls]
[laughs]
It's a Vampire Lord!
I've read about 'em, but I've
never actually seen one!
He does everything
I tell him to.
You couldn't ask
for a more perfect man!
[laughs]
Let's do this!
Release!
[yells]
Why didn't he release?
Because the Blue Troll hasn't
had enough time to recover yet.
I love playing offense.
You don't mind if
I go first, do you?
[hisses]
Dark Dragon Knight!
[ACE gasps]
[BOTH yelling]
[grunts]
[OUKA barks]
Ouka! Use Inferno Blast!
[OUKA grunting]
[barks]
[VAMPIRE LORD growls]
[sighs]
Is that all you've got?
How disappointing,
I expected more.
Oh, well.
[VAMPIRE LORD grunts]
[OUKA squeaks]
[ACE]
Ouka!
[OUKA whines]
[ACE whimpers]
There we go! I know that look!
Let me send a little
more pain your way!
[VAMPIRE LORD yells]
[TAMAZO] Do something! You can't
just run away from him!
I know that!
[VAMPIRE LORD growls]
Looks like Ace is
afraid to make a move.
Dark creatures are
vulnerable to Light!
[FAIRLION squeaks]
Fairlion!
[TAMAZO]
Five combos, Tama!
[FAIRLION squeals]
[VAMPIRE LORD grunts]
Awesome!
[hisses]
[gasps]
The attack didn't stop him?!
It's like I told you!
I've got an immortal Studmon!
There is no way you can
bring him down, kid!
[laughs]
[screams]
She's scaring me...
Why don't I spice
things up a little bit?
Vampire Lord, prepare
Attack Stance Dark, please!
Engage!
[VAMPIRE LORD growls]
[FAIRLION screams]
A life or death struggle.
For a Guild Dragon Caller,
that's just
another day on the job!
I get excited just
talking about it!
Back off!
[CHARO grunts]
Charo!
Hey, eyes over here, sweetie.
[ACE grunts]
[VAMPIRE LORD grunts]
[TAMAZO]
Ace!
Aw... I thought you'd
put up more of a fight.
But with such a useless team,
I'm not surprised it was quick.
It's always like this. Always...
[BOYS laughin]
[CHARO grunts]
Beat it, loser!
You can't even see the Drops,
so you'd only slow us down!
Aw! You gonna cry?
Check it out! More drops!
[BOYS laughing]
I won't cry...
[sobs]
[chirping]
[whistles]
You'll stay with me
won't you... Enju?
[ENJU chirps]
[laughs]
[CHARO panting]
[whistles]
Hi, Enju!
[MORIGANNON roras]
[gasps]
[ENJU squeaks]
[CHARO gasps]
[CHARO] If I had the strength,
I could've saved him...
[groans softly]
Hey! Wake up! Ace!
You'll die if you sleep, Tama!
[whistling]
[CHARO]
Ace... please wake up!
Now, now. That's cheating.
[CHARO gasps]
Naughty boys like you
need to be punished.
[whimpers]
[MORGAN gasps]
[ACE grunts]
I won't let you pick on Charo...
--Leave him alone...!
--Ace!
He's back with a vengeance!
[ACE growls]
[yells]
You okay, Charo?
Yeah!
Huh. So that's what
happens when you try.
Looks like somebody is
finally taking this seriously!
Or have you grown to enjoy
the taste of suffering?
[ACE]
Hmph.
[MORGAN]
Hm? Hmph. That's it.
The look I want to
wipe off your face!
[hisses]
Ace! Be careful!
If his next strike hits us,
we're done for, Tama!
This battle isn't over yet.
Do you hear me?
Your team is still with you!
Yeah! With all of them
helping out, we can do this!
[TAMAZO] Count me in on
this next round, partner!
Okay, Cross-On, Tama!
Oh! Awesome!
Cute.
Cross-On!
[yells]
Your Soul Armor's skill
is ready! Activate it!
Now. Dark Dragon Knight, go!
[gasps]
Fairlion!
[FAIRLION squeaks]
[VAMPIRE LORD grunts]
[OUKA barks]
[gasps]
Way to go, Tama!
[OUKA grunts]
No! Ouka!
That was a big mistake!
[VAMPIRE LORD growls]
I won't let you! Gungnir Feast!
'Kay, let's go, Tamazo!
Armor Skill! Fire becomes wood!
Now!
[yells]
[VAMPIRE LORD yells]
No! You can still
fight, can't you?!
Oh, come on,
you're embarrassing me!
I think we won.
We've passed the Guild's test.
[ACE] And I couldn't have
done it without you guys!
[OUKA squeaks]
[DARK DRAGON KNIGHT grunts]
You were brilliant!
You've really figured out how
to use your monster's powers!
[VAHATON] You've used your
Soul Armor's leader skill
to make the most out of your
Dragon-type monster's attacks.
And I especially liked the way
you and Tamazo worked together.
Nice!
Well, it was a total sink
or swim kinda thing.
And thank you. You really saved
my skin back there, Charo!
Ace...
[METAL]
Heartwarming!
This beautiful
affirmation of friendship
brings a tear to my eye!
Sadly, Ace is disqualified.
--[ACE] What?
--CHARO] Huh?
Disqualified? What for?
You heard the rules
in the beginning.
That was a one-on-one,
live or die battle, guys!
Your friends helping
you was very sweet,
but technically cheating.
So, you failed.
What?! But Ace is the one
who did all the fighting!
--Is he for real, Vahaton?!
--[CHARO sobs]
[VAHATON] If that's what the
rules say, then I suppose so.
Hey, you were one
step from the win.
Not bad for your first time.
That brings today's exam
to a close, and sadly,
no participants were
able to claim victory.
Without further ado, our
staff has come to escort
all non-members
from the premises!
[ACE, CHARO gasping]
[screaming]
Wait, what's up with these...?
I don't know but...
it ain't good...
[giggles] Better luck next time!
The door's that-a-way!
[ALL scream]
Until next time!
[GARNET]
Bye-bye, boys!
[rockets whistling]
[TAMAZO]
Ka-blooie! [laughs]
So you lost, huh?
Were you holding back
because he was a kid?
[MORGAN sighs] No, I planned
to play around with him
for a little while.
But those eyes... they
looked just the same as his.
So I had to take him seriously.
The flow of the Drops
is nice and gentle.
The Drop Impact
seems to have dissipated.
But we can't lower
our guards just yet.
Drop contamination is
causing these disturbances
to occur all around the world.
I'll go scope out the area.
You can go report to Vahaton.
[LANCE]
Hmph. Why do I have to?
I think he wants to see you.
You should visit him
once in a while.
[DEVI] Hah! Master Vahaton is
really counting on you,
isn't he, Master Lance?
It's almost as if
he thinks of you as
his actual son or
somethin', Devi.
[LANCE]
Quiet down.
[ANGENE] Quite beautiful today,
if I say so myself!
[VAHATON] Why, thank you!
I'm flattered.
Don't be silly, old man!
I was talking about the Drops.
I remember how it always
used to be like this.
The Drops had a
certain airiness to them,
which I found invigorating!
[VAHATON] Yes. Back when
we were both much younger.
Drops are the planet's energy
in a more tangible form.
They bring life to our world.
But now, they pose a threat.
It's as if the planet is
trying to tell us something.
We Ancients don't have
quite enough power to keep
the Drops under control like
we did back in the old days.
But there's still some hope!
The next generation
will take our place!
The Guild Dragon Callers--
and Ace, too!
[LANCE gasps]
Devi...
[VAHATON] King may have
disappeared long ago,
but he forged some
solid paths in his time.
He set an example for the other
Dragon Callers on how to live.
And I think young Ace is already
following in his footsteps!
Even though he apparently
failed the exam?
Think of it as an opportunity
for him to grow stronger.
[sighs] Well, I suppose it's
about time I was heading home.
Until next time.
Nice to see you again, Lance.
[VAHATON] Oh! Lance! You've
finally come back to visit me!
I don't need to follow
footsteps to find my way.
[VAHATON]
Oh, but Lance...
King abandoned his mission,
and then he disappeared.
We're in the middle of a crisis,
and this hero of yours
is nowhere to be found!
[VAHATON groans]
Dragonoids are more
than capable,
and we're actually here.
[DEVI]
We'll take our leave now, Devi.
Is this the tree
from the other day?
Yeah, that's right. This tree's
kinda like a memento of my dad.
[gasps]
I just have to plant
one and it'll grow?
[KING] I'll find the
perfect spot to plant it.
[ACE] It's proof my dad
remembered the promise
he made to me back then.
He planted the seed here for me.
Wow. That's pretty
cool. I can hardly believe
the thing's still standing after
that last monster
attack came through!
Even though I failed the exam,
I feel connected to my dad
through this tree,
and I know he'd be proud
of how far I've come.
It's like he's watching
over me, and believes in me.
[CHARO]
Mm-hmm. I believe in you!
Thanks, Charo.
[LANCE]
So this is where you've been.
[CHARO]
Lance...
Thanks for saving us
the other day.
[LANCE] Dragoza Island
is for dragonoids.
I'll do what it takes
to keep it safe.
You outsiders should
keep out of the way!
And you should mind
your manners!
Why do you dislike outsiders?
Keep quiet, kid!
You might learn something.
I'll explain it to you.
Master Lance is a
genuine dragonoid, Devi.
Which means he's not a
normal human being
like you and your friend are,
you understand?!
Dragonoid?
I'll have you know, Ace here is
not just any normal human being!
He's more of the
persistent, weakling kind!
I'd say you're being
something short
of charitable to Ace right now.
You wanna rumble,
you softboiled punk?!
I sure do,
burnt marshmallow!
Come. Let's go.
Wait a sec!
I'm not helpless, okay?
There's gotta be something I can
do that would help you out!
Of course. You can
go back to Vienna City.
[ACE]
What?!
Now stay outta my way.
Shoo, Devi.
Tama!
Where are you all going, huh?
[gasps] Grandma. I wanna
go learn more about our world.
And about the Drops--
how they work.
So I've decided to leave
Crocus and visit some
of the other areas to
further my training.
There's still a lot for me
to learn, so I'm going, too!
Tamazo, too, Tama!
Good luck, Ace. Your power
to control Drops is a gift,
always use it
to protect the innocent.
Keep that in mind wherever
your path takes you.
[ACE]
Hm.
[CHARO] I say we should
go somewhere a little bit
warmer next. How about we
make our way to the fire city?
Tama!
Oh! You're so soft and cuddly,
I'm gonna freaking die!
[ACE]
Ms. Herriot!
I brought this.
You left it behind.
[CHARO gasps] Thank you!
I was afraid that it was lost!
I'm sorry about
my little sister.
It might not seem like it,
but she's actually
pretty sweet at heart...
...I think.
You think, huh?
She might be a couple
screws loose upstairs,
but all in all
she's pretty good.
But even though I'm
her twin sister,
I still don't have any idea
what's going through her head.
You guys aren't alike in the
slightest, so it makes sense.
Yup.
Come take the exam
again sometime.
And, if you
really want training,
I've got plenty of
exercises to make you tough!
[BOTH laugh]
Thanks for your offer.
What's with the attitude?!
Harness your spirit!
Tama!
When she gets that
look in her eyes,
she's as scary as her twin!
[yells] Let's get
outta here, Tama!
Thanks! See you around!
[TAMAZO]
C'mon, Tama!
Thanks Ms. Harriet!
See ya later!
Show the world you got guts!
You hear me?!
[ACE, CHARO]
Yes, ma'am, we will!
[ACE] Here we are,
in the Fire City, Geyser!
What is the
Dragon Caller's mission?
Wait. A part-time job?
Are you kidding me?
Next time!
"A Man from Geyser."
Dragon Callers in Geyser
are hot with passion!