[ACE] After our
adventure in Vienna City,
we reported back to Libria,
and then headed off to the
Sand City to begin our training.
We're gonna
need all we can get
if we're going to enter
the upcoming Battle Cup.
Vegahs, the Sand City
oasis, tama!
Whoa! Look at that!
This says it's a town devoted
to entertainment and tourism!
A show-biz city where
people's dreams come true!
But while the main streets
are shiny and glamorous,
the back streets are rougher
areas and should be avoided.
Yeah, whatever.
I dare some fool to try
comin' at me, the Tiger!
Hey! Where's Tamazo?
--[crashing]
--[TAMA screaming]
Never ever go check out
the back streets, tama!
[ALL sigh]
Ah! These are azaleahs! Cool!
It's been forever!
That taste brings
back some memories!
Ugh, that's gross!
Is it okay to eat?
You better stop before
you get a stomach ache.
Man, I can't believe you guys
are acting like such babies!
Entetsu...?
[sighs]
What am I sayin'?
There's no reason he'd
be all the way out here.
[ENTETSU pants]
[DRAGON CALLER A] Hey,
if you could have your pick
of any Soul Armor right now,
what would you choose?
I'd probably have
to go with either
Horus or Berserk's Soul Armor.
Dude, nice choices!
And I think the ladies would
really appreciate the look.
Man, all I have right now
is a dumb Woodsie.
Huh? You should
appreciate Woodsie more!
Those guys are adorable.
I wish I had one myself!
I'll tell you what
I don't want, though.
An Entetsu.
[ENTETSU sighs]
[DRAGON CALLER A]
Entetsu's Soul Armor stinks!
I'd look really lame in it.
[DRAGON CALLER B]
Yeah, anybody would.
[DRAGON CALLER A]
I'd rather wear nothing
than Entetsu's Soul Armor.
Time to go for
the top in Vegahs, baby!
Calm down, tama!
So, where do we go?
Anywhere that isn't
the back streets...?
Hey, we should check out
the underground battle arena!
What's a battle arena?
That's where the Dragon
Caller battles take place.
it's a must-see attraction
here in Vegahs!
Yeah! Sounds fun!
[CROWD cheers]
The crowd's really pumped!
Go, Aget! Go, Aget!
[yells]
Prepare to receive
my just punishment!
[CROWD cheers]
Goooooooo! Aget!
[CROWD]
Aget! Aget! Aget!
[AGET]
Ow...
[groans]
My poor aching hip!
[knocking]
That was a really great
fight today, Mister Aget!
Would you possibly be available
to fight again this weekend?
Mr. Apollo seems to
have caught a cold
and sadly had to withdraw.
That hack Apollo
should be covering for me!
No, thank you.
Could you please help us out?!
Everybody who's anybody
knows Aget is the only
real Dragon Caller
Hero in this town!
You make Apollo look
like a total chump!
I can't argue with you there,
but I'm afraid I have
plans this weekend.
Justice never
slumbers, after all.
Oh, well, that's too bad.
Especially since the purse
has been tripled,
and you get to pick
your own opponent, but...
I guess I'll look elsewhere.
Fine.
If it'll really help you guys
out, then you can count me in.
Wow, you mean it?
A true hero could
never ignore someone
who's in distress!
[BOYS laughing]
[AGET]
Oh, man.
Hmm...
[AGET grunts]
[AGET] My hip is killing me!
And my joints ache!
Huh?
[BOY B gasps]
It's Mister Aget!
How awesome!
[AGET]
Huh?
[BOY C]
That's so mean!
[BOY B sobs]
[AGET chuckles]
[AGET] Now I've got to
find some sucker to fight
that I can easily beat.
--[TIGER] Mr. Aget...?
--[AGET] Hmm?
[TIGER squeals]
You're really him!
You're the big-shot Dragon
Caller hero, Mister Aget!
[gasps]
Sir!
Pleeeeeeeease,
pick a hand to shake!
[AGET]
He seems like a total idiot.
[AGET] Ahem. You'll have
to excuse me, I'm busy.
Hmm? You kids
are Dragon Callers?
Oh, yeah!
We're three Dragon Caller
buddies out to see the world!
[AGET] He did say I can pick
my own opponent to face
in the fight.
So, have any of you young
bucks received a Soul Armor yet?
Huh? I have.
Ace here even got
an Ancient Dragon Knight
for his Soul Armor!
[AGET]
Ancient Dragon Knight?
Dude, I wish I had
a souped-up mega-cool
Soul Armor just
like my man Ace's!
Maybe I'll find one
lying around here somewhere.
[AGET]
He really is an idiot!
Soul Stones are the
embodiment of a monster's soul!
And the only way to get
one of those is for a monster
to respect your
strength of character!
In conclusion, you don't
find them "lying around"!
So then, you don't have
a Soul Armor yet, young man?
Well. He had a Soul Armor,
but it was made of cardboard.
Pipe down, would ya?
The days of my cardboard suit
of armor are over.
I'm rocking "Soul Armor:
None" right now.
[AGET]
He's perfect!
Welcome, boys...
...to the great
Sand City of Vegahs!
It's so nice to see
another Dragon Caller in town!
Would you care to tag along
for a leisurely drive
around the city?
Can we really?!
It's a great way
to see the sights!
Ah! Hold on!
Hasn't anyone ever told you not
to get into cars with strangers?
But he's not a stranger,
though, his name is Mister Aget.
[ACE]
What should we do?
[TIGER]
Are you kidding? We join him!
Fine, then. To each his own.
Don't be that way.
I'm sorry sir.
I can't believe my buddies
shot down your friendly offer!
But, sadly, they're real dumb.
[AGET] It actually kinda
works out better this way.
Huh?
Look over there!
That statue is
a symbol of our city.
Huh...? Ah! That is so money!
I love this town!
--[TIGER] Cheers!
--[AGET] Cheers!
--[AGET] So, my friend--
--[TIGER] You can call me Tiger.
What would you say if
I told there's a real easy way
to make mega bucks
in just a few hours?
Wha...?
There's a
big battle scheduled at
the underground
arena this weekend.
And the winner of
that battle will get paid
a whole lot of money.
Seriously?
I just so happen
to be looking for someone
to face off against
me in the arena.
You in?
You mean... me, you?
No way! I'm not a match
for you, Mister Aget, sir!
Naturally, I will be victorious.
And if you do your part to make
sure that's how it goes down,
I can certainly make it
worth your while.
Wait, what are you saying?
All you have to do is
throw the fight,
and I'll make sure you
walk away with 30 percent
of the prize money.
How's that sound?
That sounds crooked.
[AGET] You're travelling
the world, aren't you?
I bet you could use
the extra cash.
It's not a bad deal
if you think about it.
But it's not good!
It means we'd have to
lie to everyone!
There's no honor
or justice in that!
I'd never be able
to forgive someone
for that kind of dishonesty!
[AGET] Curses! An idiot
with a moral code!
[CHILDREN gasping, laughing]
Huh?
[AGET] On the final stop of our
tour is the city's orphanage.
[TIGER gasps]
[GIRL A]
Look, it's Mister Aget!
[BOY D] You're my favorite-est
Dragon Caller hero, sir!
I had planned to
donate the prize money
to the orphanage,
because they could frankly use
all the help they can get.
Maybe it was
just wishful thinking,
but I really wanted
to make a difference
in those kid's lives.
The kids look up to me
as a Dragon Caller hero,
and I also know how excited
they'd be if the purse money
went to buying them
some new toys.
But you're right, Tiger.
I shouldn't do something bad,
even if something good
will come from it.
It's dishonest,
just like you said.
Forget I even asked.
Is it still bad if your
intentions are just, though?
Okay. I'm in!
Forget about it, kid!
You were right.
It's a bad thing to do!
And even though their
lives would surely improve,
the orphans wouldn't
want dirty money!
But we don't have to tell them!
It can be our
little secret, I promise!
I'm with you, Mister Aget!
If you insist, then...
...we have a deal!
Let's shake!
[TIGER grunts]
This is... so touching.
I can't-- [sobs]
[AGET]
And this is why I love idiots!
[ACE] You're really battling in
the underground arena?
That doesn't seem
like a very good idea.
Who knows what kinda tricks
Aget is gonna try to pull?
Hey, Mister Aget
isn't a bad man.
How can you be so certain?
Didn't you just meet him?
I could tell by
the look in his eyes.
It was the same look
Entetsu had that day.
Entets-who?
Entetsu, huh?
That's the name of a monster.
[TIGER] That's right.
And he saved my life.
[ACE]
A monster did?
Oh, yeah.
It all happened back when
I couldn't see drops yet.
There was a nearby cave
that was lousy with monsters.
and the adults warned us
all to never go in there.
But I went anyway,
to snack on the honeydew
from the azaleahs that only
grew inside the cave.
It turned out the cave
was Entetsu's den!
[ENTETSU growls]
[TIGER] Entetsu charged right
for me with his powerful horns!
[TIGER grunting]
[TIGER]
Are you kiddin' me?!
[TIGER grunting]
[TIGER groans]
I'll beat you, but first
we've gotta get outta here!
[ENTETSU growls]
[pants]
[grunts]
[TIGER]
Ow, that one hurt!
[grunting]
No! Not like this!
I refuse to go
down without a fight!
[TIGER groans]
[ENTETSU grunts]
You...
[gasps]
[TIGER]
Come on. He needs my help.
Entetsu!
[ENTETSU growls]
[gasps]
Hey, we did it!
I can see drops now
because of you!
Thank you!
Your antler will heal, won't it?
[ENTETSU sighs]
[gasps]
Wow, he sounds
like a cool monster!
Right? And I swear, Mr. Aget had
the very same look in his eyes
as Entetsu did on that day.
I can read people
just by lookin' them
square in the eye.
Well, if you feel
that strongly about it,
we wish you the best of luck!
Yeah, you have our full support!
[TIGER] I'm gonna go on
a little nighttime run.
I'll see ya guys!
All right! I guess we'll
catch up with you later on.
Cool!
[gasps]
[TIGER]
Entetsu! I hope you remember me.
I, uh... became
a Guild Dragon Caller.
I even have my own D-Gear...
And I'm battling
Mister Aget tomorrow!
My friends will
be there watching.
It's funny, actually.
We were just talking
over dinner about
what a great monster you are!
What's wrong?
[ENTETSU sighs]
[CROWD murmuring]
Today's the big day!
I'm getting nervous!
[AGET]
Listen up.
When you do that,
I'll counter like this.
But above all,
we've got to make it look real!
So hit me with
about three combos!
It'll start looking
like I'm going to lose.
But no matter how hard it gets,
a true hero never gives up.
I'll shout out "Receive
my just punishment,"
and then unleash
my ultimate final attack!
And then, you take a fall.
Hang on.
Are you listening?
[gasps] Oh, yes, sir.
You can count on me!
[ANNOUNCER A] He's a big-shot
rookie all the way from Geyser.
Welcome, Tiger!
Time to shoot for the very top!
Tiger!
Go get him!
Go for the top!
[ANNOUNCER A] Here comes
the patron Dragon Caller hero
of the great
Sand City of Vegahs. Aget!
Prepare to receive
my just punishment!
[GIRLS screaming]
[bell rings]
Okay! Release!
Now! Release!
[RED GIANT roars]
[AGDRALL grunts]
Agdrall! Strike!
[AGET]
Mm-mm.
Oops. Not just yet.
Something seems wrong.
It's like he isn't
trying to shoot
for the top at all!
[TIGER grunts]
[AGDRALL yelps]
[RED GIANT roars]
[ANNOUNCER A] Tiger barely
puts a combo together!
[AGET chuckles]
[TIGER growls]
[TIGER]
Not like this!
I'm not going down without
a fight, you hear me? Never!
[sighs]
Just wait.
I'll be a Dragon Caller
for the Guild.
And I'll climb right to the top!
I'm gonna show
all those naysayers
just how wrong they are!
I'm gonna prove myself!
I won't leave
any room for doubt!
The top spot or bust.
[RED GIANT growls]
My final attack!
[ANNOUNCER A]
Oh, wow!
We're looking at a
whopping eight combos!
This looks to be a
devastatingly massive attack!
[ANNOUNCER A]
Oh, but what's this?
A monster has forced
his way into the battle!
Entetsu?!
What's wrong, buddy?!
C'mon, stay with me!
Ah, huh?
He's Entetsu?
Here, take this!
[ENTETSU growls]
But if you don't,
you're gonna disappear!
[ENTETSU pants]
[ENTETSU]
This is it, child.
What are you saying...?
I know, you mean
our long-waited battle!
All right!
I promise to come at you
with everything I've got
after this battle has ended!
[ENTETSU]
I give my soul to you...
Use it and be safe...
We'll go to the top...
together...
Of course we will...
Is that a Soul Stone?
So, then Entetsu accepted Tiger?
Tama! Tama-tama-tama?
--Ta-ama!
--[yelps]
What did he just do?!
What the heck, Tamazo?!
Tama. ArmorDrop, tama!
[TAMAZO]
TA-DAAAH!
Is this... Entetsu's Armor?
What's wrong?
Did you lose
your fighting spirit?
[ANNOUNCER A] Umm, it
appears Tiger has forfeited,
so I declare Aget
to be the winner.
[TIGER]
Not yet. The name's Tiger!
And I won't stop
till I reach the top!
[ANNOUNCER A]
Oh, yeah!
It looks like
the battle is back on!
I'll win this thing either way.
Let's go, Entetsu!
Cross-On time!
Wait, wha--?
Is that Entetsu's Soul Armor?
He looks so lame!
You can forget about
the concept of impossible!
Because I'm here to make
my dreams come true!
All right! Let's rock, Agdrall!
[AGDRALL roars]
[RED GIANT grunting]
[screams]
Yeah! Entetsu's soul and Tiger's
heart are working together
as one force!
Wow, Tiger's
Soul Armor is impressive!
Hey, back to
the routine we rehearsed!
You're supposed
to lose, remember?
Here we go again!
[AGDRALL ROARS]
That's Entetsu's Soul Armor!
It might be okay.
You bet it is!
He's got a second wind!
You little twit!
How dare you be so cocky?!
Entetsu, your blazing
soul is firing up my own!
Here's to the top!
Receive my just punishment!
Fire Horn!
[ANNOUNCER A] He's activated
Entetsu's leader skill,
Fire Horn. Now, his monster
has boosted attack power!
[AGDRALL roars]
[AGET screams]
[TIGER]
I am so sorry, Mister Aget!
[AGET] I was supposed
to win this fight!
I was just responding
to Entetsu's feelings.
If anyone can understand,
it's you, Mister Aget.
[AGET]
Of course I don't.
Are you okay? I feel terrible!
So, I've decided
the prize money isn't mine!
It's all yours, Mr. Aget!
[AGET]
Oh, really?
Well, if that's the case, Tiger,
I guess I'll have
to let it slide.
Wow, you mean it? That's good!
But then again,
I always knew you had
a big heart, didn't I?
[AGET laughs]
Great. Hand it over.
You just sit there
and get better!
I already donated
all of it to the orphanage,
just like you wanted
from the very beginning!
All under the name
MR. Aget, of course!
[AGET]
You did what with the money?
[TIGER] Mr. Aget was so happy
to hear the good news!
Y'know I guess I did all right!
Yeah, you were
really cool today, Tiger!
I actually respect you!
Yeah, well, it's all
thanks to Entetsu!
Hey, Tamazo.
How in the world did you
change the Soul Stone
to an Armor Drop back there?
That's right.
It meant we didn't have to
go back to Miss Sally
to ask for help.
[TAMAZO] It was Sally
herself who taught me
how to do it, tama!
The strands of
fate wove us together, tama.
For real?
Tamazo's full of surprises!
All things are
possible with me, tama!
[ACE, TAMAZO]
Believe in Tamazo!
[laughs]
Oh! Hey, Aget!
Oh, no! Tiger!
[TIGER]
See you later!
And thanks again
for showing me around!
Why don't we fight each
other for real next time,
whaddaya say, pal?
"Next time"?
I'm totally
coming back to Vegahs!
[AGET]
No! Just stay away!
[CHARO]
I'm so happy for Tiger.
He got Entetsu's Soul Armor!
Now it's my turn!
I've got to find my
dream-monster, too!
But he's at the haunted
house deep in the forest?
Next time:
"Charo and the Haunted Forest."
It's probably just
a trick of the light.