[NARRATOR]
For untold centuries,
there have been powerful
warriors who fought against
the various crises
that threatened our world.
They harnessed the power
of the monsters,
and forged a bond which
eased the planet's anger.
They were the Dragon Callers.
Dragon Callers are born
with the special power
to bridge the gap
between the realms
of nature, mankind,
and monsters.
When fear and hatred contaminate
the elements that surround us,
the Dragon Callers will
rise up with their monsters,
and restore balance
to our world.
[CHARO'S MOM]
Bon appetit, boys!
This looks yummy!
I'm gonna do two forks
worth of damage!
And please, feel free to
eat as much as you'd like!
Tiger's not here.
I'll eat for him!
For friendship!
[CHARO'S DAD]
Isn't it tasty, Charo?
[CHARO]
Yes!
Make sure to eat well,
so you can grow bigger
than me one day!
Our son's fine
just the way he is.
My little boy.
[CHARO]
Uh?
Stop it, Mom.
This is so embarrassing.
[ACE, CHARO'S DAD,
CHARO'S MOM laugh]
[CHARO]
Would you stop laughing?
[CHARO'S MOM]
Okay, okay.
[ACE]
Hi, Mom. How're you?
I'm in the Wood City
of Libria right now.
Charo's house is here,
and his mom and dad are
letting us stay with them.
I'm still training to be the
best Dragon Caller I can be,
but it takes time.
I gathered a bunch, tama!
[ACE] There's never a lack of
excitement, that's for sure.
[gasps]
Those fruit look tasty.
[ACE]
Tamazo's doing fine too.
He's still as noisy
and carefree as ever.
But at least he's loyal.
He's never left my side once.
Feels like ages since
I left Vienna City behind
and headed out to make
my own way in the world.
[ACE]
Drops.
[TAMAZO]
Uh! Ace!
[ACE]
Now that's an egg!
[gasps]
[TAMAZO]
Tama!
Stop that! Would ya cut it out?
Gimme a break!
[yells]
[ACE]
After I met Tamazo,
I learned something
about myself.
That I had the abilities of a
Dragon Caller, just like my dad,
and that's when my life changed.
What are these?
That kid.
He formed these Drops
from that distance?
[ACE] Me, a Dragon Caller?
Get serious!
[CHARO]
I am serious!
I think you've got
exactly what it takes.
Someone with your kind of
power can't just stay here.
Be one of the protectors
of our world.
Protector.
Exactly!
So that's why you should come
to Dragoza Island with me,
and then we can both study
to become Dragon Callers.
[ACE]
So I'm going to Dragoza Island.
[LENA]
It's okay to want to go.
[ACE] I'm sorry that I left
you alone so suddenly,
but I had to.
I miss you, Mom.
I wanted to learn all about
Dragon Callers, Drops,
and the world we live in,
and I had to leave
home to do it.
I see it. Dragoza!
[ACE] Every day on Dragoza
Island has been interesting,
to say the least.
[gasps]
Grandma, I'm here.
Is that really you, Ace?
You've grown so much since
the last time I saw you!
Take this.
A D-Gear?
This particular one
belonged to your father.
It was his D-Gear, Ace,
and it should help
guide you on your path
to become a great Dragon
Caller, just like he was.
[CHARO] That's the real thing!
Can I hold it?
[ACE laughs]
Yeah. Why not? I don't know
how to use it anyway.
[CHARO] For starters,
you're going to need to get
a monster Egg Drop
just to get it functional.
What's an Egg Drop?
That's what it's called
when a monster
takes the form of a Drop.
All you have to do is stick
the Drop in your D-Gear
and then you can
summon that monster
to fight for you as an ally.
[ACE]
Okay. How do I get an Egg Drop?
[CHARO]
Uhh...
The Dragon Caller's Guide says
that the monster
has to accept you.
Then it'll turn into an
Egg Drop all on its own.
Hey, listen to me.
It's not just dangerous to stay
out here all by yourself,
it's also lonely.
Would you lend me your power?
We'd make a great team.
[roars]
Let's do this, Ouka!
[ACE]
Now! Lend me your power!
Release!
[ACE]
Not long after I got my D-Gear,
I found the first
monster for my team.
[yells]
[ACE] Thanks to Charo
and Tamazo's help,
I was able to become
a real Dragon Caller.
Or so I thought.
I know, but why did you want
that Soul Armor so badly,
do you think?
[ACE] Well, if I could
equip the armor,
then it would make me a stronger
Dragon Caller, wouldn't it?
Tama?
[CHARO]
He's an Ancient Dragon Knight!
[ACE]
We've gotta do something!
[roars]
[CHARO gasps]
Hurry, you've gotta
turn into an Egg Drop!
[ANCIENT DRAGON KNIGHT]
It's too late.
But I can still put
my soul to good use.
[SALLY] That's a lovely Soul
Stone you have there, Ace.
[ACE]
Hey, Sally.
It's undeniable proof that
the Ancient Dragon Knight
has accepted you.
I am a priestess.
My duty is to bestow the
energy from the Soul Stone
to a worthy Dragon Caller.
In this way, new
Soul Armor is created
and we fulfill our purpose.
[ACE]
Hey, Tamazo,
how in the world did you
change the Soul Stone
to an Armor Drop back there?
[CHARO]
That's right.
It meant we didn't
have to go back
to Miss Sally to ask for help.
[TAMAZO]
It was Sally herself
who taught me how
to do it, tama!
The strands of fate
wove us together, tama.
For real?
Tamazo's full of surprises.
All things are possible
with me, tama!
Soul Armor.
[CHARO gasps]
I like it! So easy-going!
And to have Soul Armor
on top of that,
I bet you're unstoppable!
I'm amped up!
Old Dragon Knight's
Code, activate!
[roars]
[yells]
[ACE yells]
Stop him!
You did it, Ace!
That was so incredible!
That monster looked real
tough, but you stomped him!
[CHARO gasps]
[CHARO]
He's huge!
The Drop Impact should go
away if I defeat him, right?
This monster's way
out of your league!
I was able to beat that
other one all by myself!
No! He's too strong!
[ACE yelling]
Hold on, Ace!
[LANCE]
Idiots.
You need to recognize
your own limitations.
[MORGAN]
A life or death struggle.
For a Guild Dragon Caller,
that's just another
day on the job.
Sadly, Ace is disqualified.
What?
Disqualified? What for?
[ACE]
After I was injured,
I realized I wasn't
strong enough yet.
[VAHATON]
King was one of the all-time
greatest Dragon Callers.
Last time it got this bad,
King had to save us all.
I couldn't believe he
dissipated a Drop Impact
of that magnitude single-handed.
My father didn't need any help?
[ACE] I also learned a lot
about my father along the way.
He was a hero who stopped
a massive Drop Impact
all by himself.
Everyone says he was a strong
and respectable Dragon Caller.
[ACE]
Yeah, that's right.
This tree's kinda like
a memento of my dad.
So I just have to plant
one and it'll grow?
Don't worry. I'll find the
perfect spot to plant it.
[ACE] It's proof my dad
remembered the promise
he made to me back then.
He planted the seed here for me.
[ACE] I've met so many
interesting people.
You must put your
whole heart into it.
[ACE gasps]
So how do I do that?
Well, perhaps that's
for you to figure out.
[ACE] I'll never forget the
people who've helped me.
[GARNET] I guess you
clowns owe me big time!
Are you being naughty
and talking back to me?
Harness your spirit!
[ACE] Or those that taught me
about being a Dragon Caller.
Your power to control
Drops is a gift.
Always use it to
protect the innocent.
Keep that in mind wherever
your path takes you.
[ACE]
It wasn't all just good times.
Lance is still an
obnoxious show-off.
He has a real knack
for being rude.
Run, you idiot!
[ACE] But in spite of it,
he still helped so much.
He saved Vienna City.
He saved me.
[ACE]
All right, it's time.
Let's get this
Guild exam started!
Our first step in becoming
Guild Dragon Callers!
This'll be your first
time, right, Charo?
This'll be Tiger's
11th time, tama.
Shut your face!
[TIGER, CHARO, ACE scream]
[ACE] I couldn't have become
a Guild Dragon Caller
without help from so many
friends along the way.
And I've only come this far
because I had them
here to support me.
[TAMAZO]
I'm pumped!
[LANCE]
They all passed.
Then that means...
We did it!
We're finally...
[ACE, TIGER, CHARO]
...Guild Dragon Callers!
[ACE laughs]
[TIGER] I can't get stronger
by just having fun.
[TIGER]
You guys!
Go for the top!
I'll see you there!
[ACE]
I have to become stronger
so that I can become the Dragon
Caller I was always meant to be.
I need to work harder.
[TAMAZO]
Ace! Ace!
Take a look at that sky, tama!
[ACE gasps]
[ACE] According to what
Master Torlie told us,
Drop Impacts occur
because this world is hurt
and trying to heal itself.
But what could be
causing it so much pain?
[TANK COMMANDER A]
Astro-Particle Cannon! Fire!
[YAMAKI]
It's my understanding
you were ordered to
capture that monster,
and since that didn't happen,
you've come here casting blame.
You certainly have a
brash attitude for a man
who clearly failed the
mission assigned to him.
If we hand it over to the
Ancient's representative,
then the Guild will
owe the SDF a favor.
And that kind of favor is
worth the property damage
the town sustained.
[LANCE] Dragoza Island
is for Dragonoids.
I'll do what it takes
to keep it safe.
You outsiders should
keep out of the way!
And you should
mind your manners!
Why do you dislike outsiders?
Keep quiet, kid.
You might learn somethin'.
I'll explain it to you.
Master Lance is a
genuine Dragonoid, devi.
Which means he's not
a normal human being
like you and your friend are,
you understand?
Dragonoid?
[ELDER A] Originally,
there was only one hot spring
here in the Fire City,
operated by a local
Dragonoid fellow.
Hearing about his success,
humans from all over
began moving here
seeking their fortunes,
each opening their
own hot spring bath.
Every time a new one opened up,
Geyser's cityscape and
the surrounding terrain
were irrevocably changed.
Now they're constantly
competing to prove
their bath house is the best.
What? Our bath is more popular!
You humans' hot springs
are so foolish.
[CHARO]
The Salamander's come back!
[TIGER]
Run for your lives, people!
Hold on!
Something's different.
He doesn't want to fight us.
I'm not sure what's wrong.
Maybe he wants to evolve.
Huh?
[CHARO] The Salamander
evolved into Ifrit!
But, Ace, how did you
know what it wanted?
I'm not really sure.
[ELDORA] You were able to calm
the Salamander's rage.
Allow me to extend my gratitude
on behalf of the
people of our city.
What's got them so upset?
They're rooting for
different candidates
to replace the Ancient.
So Master Tinbell announced
that he would step down
as Ancient of Wood.
He's named two of his
most capable students
as the finest
potential candidates
to serve as his replacement.
We shall hold a
battle to determine
which of these contenders
will be the next Ancient.
[VILLAGERS cheer]
The candidate who claims
victory over the other
will be named my successor.
Dude, what the heck
is going on here?!
[ACE]
Is it a Drop Impact?
It's still at the
stage before that!
[CHARO] Which means that you
can do something about it,
right, Torlie?
[TORLIE]
Master Tinbell could've done it,
but I can't.
If we don't do something soon,
the forest will be destroyed!
[TORLIE]
Master!
Grant me the strength
to finish this!
Release!
[yells]
[ALL gasp]
It worked!
[roars]
[CHARO] Oh, wow! That was
incredible, Master Torlie!
[VAHATON]
Marvelous work!
Torlie was finally able to
release Master Tinbell.
He more than qualifies!
I rescind my complaints.
I'm amazed by how
quickly human beings
can adapt to solve problems,
unlike Dragonoids.
That's the power of humans.
[ELDORA] That Ace boy, he seems
a lot like his father, King.
He was a brave Dragon Caller
who could understand
the feelings of his monsters.
I guess Ace takes
after his father.
There will be an increase in
activity in the coming days.
So it's fortunate
that the mayor
has thrown his full support
behind our initiative.
Then he's finally
decided to take action.
Sure took his sweet time.
All right, let's start the test.
[RESEARCHER A]
Sir!
Well, so far, we've only
heard rumors, devi,
but someone is making a fortune
selling the Egg Drops
of rare monsters
on the black market, devi.
[LANCE]
These criminals trick monsters
and have them turn
into Egg Drops,
only to sell them off
to the highest bidder.
[DEVI] But we can't
seem to find any clues
that would help us shut
their operation down, devi.
[ACE]
They have to be stopped.
We have to do something.
I'll help you out!
Tama!
Hold on!
I wanna help you save
all of your friends!
I promise to set them free.
Now, let's fight him together.
[ACE]
White Dragon.
Go! Release!
[LOGAN gasps]
I'm not gonna lose.
Not to someone who doesn't care
about monsters' feelings.
I refuse. You hear me?
[CHARO]
Ace!
Uh, Master Torlie?
We decided to come
up to this hill
to better monitor the Drop
situation as it develops.
But the flow of Drops doesn't
seem to have changed much.
How 'bout you?
What were you doing?
I was just putting together an
e-mail to send home to my mom.
But I'm having a hard time
putting all my
thoughts to words.
And, Master Torlie,
I've gotta know.
Is our world really
going to die?
[BOTH gasp]
There has to be a way for us to
finally stop the Drop Impacts!
Perhaps so. But I fear
it won't be easy.
It's very difficult
to restore balance
when the magnitude of the
effect is on a global scale.
If we even can.
Oh, no.
So we can't do anything
but sit back
and watch everything get worse?
We must continue
communicating with our planet.
Only then can we try to calm
the Drop Impact cycle.
And in so doing,
find the key to saving
the home of mankind,
Dragonoids, and monsters alike.
Those were the words of
a great Dragon Caller.
He endeavored to find a solution
to the Drop Impact problem.
Until one day,
he mysteriously disappeared
while searching for the answer.
So this Dragon Caller
you're quoting...?
I suppose you've heard of King.
[ACE gasps]
[TORLIE] I stumbled across
a few of the research papers
he had written when
I was looking through
the Drop Impact record files.
His words, they resounded with
hopeful language and tone,
as if nothing could
bring him down at all.
You mean he was
never one to give up.
Whatever happened to him,
wherever he was sent,
he might still be fighting
to stop the Drop Impact.
I have a feeling you
might be right.
Even in darkness, as long
as you keep moving forward,
there's bound to be a few
rays of hope eventually.
I've spent so much of
my time just thinking about
different ways to
become stronger,
instead of getting out
there and doing it.
That was just what I needed
to hear. Thanks, Torlie.
I'm gonna train even
harder from now on.
Until I'm the best
Dragon Caller I can be.
Good.
Tama! That's the spirit!
Now that that's settled,
it's off to the next city, tama!
That's right!
The path to becoming a
renowned Dragon Caller
isn't predetermined for anyone.
You must walk the path
you believe is right, Ace.
Best of luck.
Yeah!
[phone chimes]
Ace!
[ACE]
"Dear Mom, I'm doing well!"
That's it?
[LENA]
Give it your best shot, Ace.
Okay, so where are
we headed off to next?
To the Light City.
The City of Exscion!
[TAMAZO]
Next episode,
we'll be visiting
Garnet's old school, tama!
It's an all-girls school,
and there are lots of new faces!
You won't want to miss it, tama!
Next time!
"Our Youthful Valkyrie."
Garnet's hidden past
is revealed, tama!