[JEST]
Enter.
I didn't pull you away
from anything did I?
No.
Devi?
Someone told me it
had been a while
since the last time
he'd seen you,
so I thought I
would call you in.
[BOY]
What's up, Devi?
Have you changed your mind?
You decide to come with me yet?
[DEVI] It's been "no" since
the first time you asked.
Now let go, devi!
Aw, come on. Please?
You seem to be
doing quite well.
I hear that you
recently saw Sonia.
Yes, and Ace as well.
[BOY]
Ace?
Is that someone I should know?
Ace is the son of King,
and like Lance here,
he has a Tamadra of his own.
Wait, King? Tamadra?
And you know him?
Humans are so foolish.
Till next time, Devi.
See ya around.
Oh, yeah? Well, not if
I see you first, devi!
He hasn't changed at all.
Try not to be too put-off
by his childish behavior.
His finer qualities
outweigh the rest,
and he's needed for
the future of our planet.
The Guild is on its way towards
collapse from the inside.
I heard that from Nudo.
So what does it mean?
Oh? He told you that?
I'm afraid what he said was true
and time, sadly,
is not on our side.
You've known this whole time?
If the Guild collapses, then
who's left to save the world?
We are, of course.
The Dragonoids were always
meant to save the world.
It's our birthright.
When the time finally comes
to ascend to our destiny,
I'm going to need
your assistance.
Can I count on you?
Yes.
[ACE] This trip to
Shining Town's been fun.
It's such a lively place!
It's known for something else.
A mighty Dragon Caller
named Star John lives here.
Star John? I've never
heard of him.
Wait, you seriously don't know?
[ACE]
Mh-hm.
Believe it or not,
but I haven't heard of
this guy either, tama.
[CHARO chuckles]
According to the rumors,
he's incredibly strong.
He's also very elusive, because
no one's ever seen him before.
But if no one's
ever seen the guy,
how do we know how strong he is?
Seems like a weird rumor.
That's actually a
very good point.
[stomach growls]
My tummy's grumbling, tama!
Time to find something yummy!
Hey, come back!
[CHARO]
Wait for us!
It's an ice cream
paradise, tama!
But look, that's
such a long line.
We're gonna have
to wait a while.
[ACE] There isn't a line
at this one over here.
I don't really feel like
ordering anything from them.
The more run-down it is,
the better the food!
Like the saying goes, quick
and bold wins the race, tama!
Why not?
[CHARO]
Huh?
Excuse me! We'd like
some ice cream.
I think I'll have
strawberry, tama!
[OWNER A]
No.
Then I'll take a
scoop of chocolate!
[OWNER A grumbles]
No!
Vanilla, caramel,
hazelnut, mint chocolate,
raspberry, cookie dough?
I'll take anything you've got!
No. No. No. No.
No!
[ALL]
Uh...
You do run an ice
cream shop, right?
Well, it ain't a ramen shop.
Would you please just
sell us some ice cream?
I don't do business if
the mood doesn't strike me.
That's been my one
and only policy
since I first opened this shop.
[ALL]
Huh?
[MAN A]
Hey! What's the big idea?
[MAN B] Yeah! Why don't
ya say somethin'?
[MAN A] Are you listening
to me, runt? Huh?
Hey! Enough! Stop ganging
up on that poor kid!
[KID]
Please help me!
I'm so scared!
[KID cries]
And who are you anyway?
This isn't any of your business!
I can handle
these goons, tama!
Tamatama Storm!
[yells]
Are we just a joke to you?!
[screams]
Please help me,
Mister Dragon Caller!
[CHARO]
Uh?
That's a D-Gear!
This kid isn't joking.
This is bad!
So what do we do?
[MAN A]
Uh.
You'll pay for this!
Yeah, you punks
better run, tama!
Hey, uh...
Thank you for saving me!
Oh, you're welcome.
Hi, my name's Charo!
And my name is--
You're Ace, right?
You know him?
Of course I do!
He's one of the fastest rising
stars in the whole Guild!
I'm such a big fan
of both Mister Ace
and Mister Tamazo, too!
Well, that's nice of you to say!
I can't believe I'm a
celebrity now, tama!
So, uh, my name's Astell!
Nice to meet you!
[TAMAZO]
Tama!
Hey now, kid! What do you
think you're doing? Let go!
I want one too!
I want my own Tamazo!
Please, Mister Ace,
you think I could keep him?
Uh, what? No. I need him.
What he said, tama!
Aww...
[ACE] So are you trying to
find Star John like we are?
I sure am!
Apparently, Star John
is supposed to be
a super strong Dragon Caller!
Yeah, we heard some rumors
pretty much to the same effect.
Except...
Except no one's ever
actually seen the guy.
Wait, what? Seriously?
I thought if I came to this
city, I'd be sure to find him!
I dream about becoming
a respected Guild
Dragon Caller one day.
I was planning
to ask Star John
if he would train me
whenever I found him.
I feel dumb.
[ACE]
Cheer up, Astell.
We'll find him together!
Wow, really?
Yeah! Right, Charo?
Sure, why not?
I mean, it's not like we're
in the middle of a mission.
Plus, it's a chance for
us to get some training
from Star John too, tama!
Good point!
Gee, I really appreciate it!
But we haven't got any
leads on his identity.
How are we ever
going to find him?
Door-to-door is
Investigation 101.
And the one clue we have is
that he's here in this town.
So that means someone somewhere
has got to know something.
I couldn't say.
I've never seen,
much less met the man.
Thanks, Mister.
We appreciate your time.
[OLD MAN A]
Hey, hold on there.
[TAMAZO]
Tama?
You seem pretty clever.
So take my advice, stop
your hunt for Star John.
Why do you say that, sir?
From what I've heard,
this Star John fellow is
an all-around bad person.
Well, like everything
related to the man,
I only know this from rumor.
But the story goes: He's such
a mighty Dragon Caller
that he has a godhead
serving under him.
A godhead?
Mophead? Letterhead?
It's an old word
that means deity.
You're liable to find
yourselves neck deep in trouble
if you decide to keep
looking for Star John.
We still don't have
any real leads.
And we still haven't gotten
any ice cream yet, tama!
We could use the break.
So ice cream it is!
Tama?
That stall wouldn't
sell us anything, tama.
Hi-ya, can I have
some ice cream?
Sorry, kid, but I'm just not
really feelin' it right now.
If you really want
some ice cream,
go wait in line
for the other shop.
Gimme some ice cream!
I already told you,
I don't feel like it, kid!
I told you I want some,
and you're gonna give
it to me right now.
[yelps]
Yeah! Sure thing! Right away!
Here, and let me say sorry again
for making you boys wait.
[ASTELL]
Thank you, Mister!
Here, help yourselves!
Tama! It's delicious!
The tart sweetness of the
strawberry perfectly marries
with the silkiness
of the vanilla, tama!
And the combination of
the bitter chocolate
and the roasted nuts
is out of this world!
That shop's ice
cream is fantastic!
Astell, how'd you get that
cranky owner guy to serve you?
I just looked him square in
the eye and asked him firmly.
You guys have been nice
enough to help me out,
I thought you deserved to
get some ice cream for it!
I see. Well, thank
you very much!
[chuckles]
So what are we going to do now?
Should we continue
asking around the town?
Man, I just don't know.
I forgot!
[ASTELL]
I just remembered I had this!
[CHARO]
You have a map?
This must be Shining Town, here,
and it looks like there's
something in the forest
at the edge of town.
[ASTELL]
Yeah!
That's where we can find a clue
to wherever Star John is hiding.
--[ACE, CHARO] What?
--[TAMAZO] Tama?!
You had this in your
pocket the entire time?
I wish you would've
remembered it sooner.
For real, tama!
[chuckles]
[ASTELL laughs]
You look silly when I do that!
My tail's not a
yo-yo string, tama!
Ace, can I please keep him?
You gotta let me have him.
Tamazo's so much fun!
Nope, I'm afraid
I still need him.
According to the map,
the clue about Star John
should be up ahead.
If he's as horrible as
that old man said he was,
and even half as strong
as the rumors claim,
then we could find ourselves
in over our heads.
Maybe, and if he really
does have a god serving him,
then he's gotta be
pretty powerful.
When I Cross-On,
I'm basically like a god,
and I serve under you, tama!
[ACE laughs]
Yeah, I guess you're right!
Star John's a Dragon
Caller just like we are!
I'm sure he'll train us once
we explain our situation.
Look at that.
[ASTELL gasps]
They're so beautiful!
Astell, wait!
[ACE]
Astell!
[ASTELL screaming]
[ASTELL]
There's a mean monster.
He came right at me!
[roars]
It's A Light Armademon!
Stand back. You're safe now.
All right, we're not
trying to hurt him.
We just need to scare him away.
Sure thing, tama!
[CHARO]
Watch out! Move!
That was a close one!
Tamatama Storm,
the Upgraded Version!
[laughs]
It looks the same as before!
How is that an upgrade?
Tamazo, that isn't gonna work!
How about this, tama?
[TAMAZO yells]
Oh, yeah!
I did it, tama.
You're gonna be
just fine, Astell.
I'm scared! I don't
wanna be here anymore!
[ASTELL cries]
[ACE]
Astell!
Where did he go, tama?
He was just a little kid.
I think all of the excitement
may have been too much for him.
Let's split up and search.
We'll go this way.
Then I guess I'll go this way.
Tama.
There he is, tama!
Astell! Hey! We were all
worried about you, kiddo!
[ASTELL]
Astell, you say?
Who's that?
What?
[TAMAZO]
Tama?
Guess you finally
found Star John.
No! You're lying!
A little kid like you just can't
be a powerful Dragon Caller
with a god for a servant, tama!
You really shouldn't
underestimate me.
That's a mistake!
A D-Gear? Then you really are--
You can say that again!
Tamazo!
Does that mean you were
lying to us all along?
I guess I was! So are you mad?
[TAMAZO] Yeah, that's a
totally mean thing to do!
[STAR JOHN laughs]
You're right, y'know.
I'm actually guilty of a
few nasty little pranks.
Like those guys.
I might've done my part
to set that in motion
before you ran in to help.
And then I gave you
some random map,
and then I ran into the woods
and antagonized that
Light Armademon.
And I'm so very, very sorry!
Nah, just kidding.
I really had my hopes up.
I mean, you're King's son,
and even a hotshot like
Lance knows you by name.
But you've been quite
a disappointment.
You didn't finish off that angry
monster I sent after you.
Maybe you'd rather
head back to town
and eat some stupid ice cream.
You're just a big softy,
which makes me think
you're never going to be
much of a Dragon Caller.
All in all, I'd say you've been
a real waste of my time!
Tama!
Step back, Tamazo!
But, Ace!
Star John isn't a monster!
We can't fight him.
No! Ace!
We're the first people
to have found you.
And now, you've shown
your true colors.
We know who Star John really is!
Stay with me, Ace!
Tamazo!
How dare you hurt him!
You realize you don't have to
just sit there and take it.
In fact, feel free to use
your monsters to attack me.
Cross-On!
Now! Release!
[yells]
Huh. Hey, is that Ancient
Dragon Knight's Soul Armor
you got there?
You can't hope to take
me on with that.
Let's go! Ouka! White Dragon!
I'll pitch in too!
Cross-On, tama!
Awesome! I'm super angry!
All right, Ace, it's time to
teach this guy a lesson!
Okay!
Come, Dark Dragon Knight,
Leviathan, and Tamazo!
Attack!
Here comes the pain!
[gasps]
What happened?
Tremble before Zeus,
the god of thunder.
A god? It's true?
[ZEUS]
No harm will come to him.
I must protect Star John.
Don't hold back now, Zeus.
Blast them all to smithereens.
Wrath of God!
No way! His attack
is too powerful!
[screams]
[STAR JOHN] I guess playtime
is over for today.
Then again, with such
a wimpy Dragon Caller
wearing such
pathetic Soul Armor,
it wasn't much of a
playtime to start with.
Hey, Tamadra!
You should consider coming
with me next time.
See ya later!
[gasps]
[CHARO]
Ace? Tamazo?
What happened to you guys?
Please, wake up!
I'm here. Who did
this to you, Ace?
It was Star John.
[CHARO gasps]
[CHARO]
Star John? So you met him?
No, it...
Where is he?
It was Astell.
He was toying with us.
He was really Star John.
[CHARO gasps]
He lied to us, tama.
I can't believe it!
He beat me.
Star John won. I lost.
He crushed me!
[ACE] I was so frustrated,
so focused on becoming stronger,
that I didn't realize
until it was too late
that the real danger was
coming straight for us.
Next time!
"Nightmare in Light City."
I will find the strength to win!