[NARRATOR]
For untold centuries,
there have been powerful
warriors who fought against
the various crises that
threatened our world.
They harnessed
the power of the monsters,
and forged a bond which
eased the planet's anger.
They were the Dragon Callers.
[NARRATOR] Dragon Callers
are born with the special power
to bridge the gap between
the realms of nature,
mankind, and monsters.
When fear and hatred contaminate
the elements that surround us...
...the Dragon Callers will
rise up with their monsters
and restore balance
to our world.
[TAMAZO]
Tama.
[BOTH gasp]
[ACE]
This is Ace.
Target spotted, over.
[LANCE] You still aren't
strong enough for this.
Just stay put and watch me.
What?
[roars]
Tama!
This guy's gettin'
super angry, tama!
And he's going up against him.
[WHITE DRAGON growls]
[TAMAZO]
Tama?
Tama.
Hi, and welcome to
the Guild Contract
Board and Information Booth.
Where the people come
to ask for assistance!
And am I right to assume
that you're Guild
Dragon Caller Ace?
Yeah, but how did you know that?
Master Jest told me.
The Ancient of Light
mentioned you specifically!
He said you were very promising!
Aw, shucks.
I don't know about that!
Someone's famous now!
Mister Big Shot!
Well, now that you're here, Ace,
we have a contract we
hoped you'd take!
[TAMAZO]
He looks scary, tama!
This dragon has been acting
quite aggressive lately,
and so we've had to
close certain roads
which has made travel
very inconvenient.
Which means you need
someone to put a stop to it.
You can count on me!
Wait, what?
Let's take on an
easier mission, tama!
I just knew we could count on
a hero like you to lend
a helping hand!
You'll be working
with Mister Lance
on this mission
as his assistant.
[gasps]
I'm his assistant?
Tama?
[ACE pants]
Tama doesn't
taste good, Mister Dragon!
And what's the big idea,
letting him spot you?
I can't help it
if my star-like qualities
shine through, tama!
[WHITE DRAGON roars]
[ACE pants, gasps]
[TAMAZO]
It's a dead-end, tama!
Then we have no choice.
It's time for us
to take a stand!
Yup!
[TAMAZO]
Tama?
I get it.
He was so scared of
Tama that he fainted!
Nuh-uh!
Dream on, Egghead!
Look closer, devi!
[LANCE]
Idiot.
Come on...
[WHITE DRAGON growls]
Look out!
Keep quiet and watch, devi!
[WHITE DRAGON growls]
They took your friends.
So, that's why you're upset.
[WHITE DRAGON sighs]
[LANCE] Don't worry,
I'll get them back for you.
I promise.
[roars]
That was awesome.
He was able to connect
with that monster so easy.
I thought
I told you not to move.
Next time, listen.
Bah! He totally
stole our thunder!
This case is now closed, devi.
I'll go ahead and
report back to the Guild
that we've completed
today's mission.
--Not yet.
--[DEVI gasps]
What? But the mission is over!
You just calmed that
dragon down, didn't you?
I need to find his
friends and bring them home.
I gave him my word.
Sounds like the work of
the trafficking organization!
Who are they?
Well, so far,
we've only heard rumors, devi.
But someone is making a
fortune selling the Egg Drops
of rare monsters on
the black market, devi.
[LANCE] These criminals
trick monsters,
and have them turn
into Egg Drops.
Only to sell them off
to the highest bidder.
[DEVI] But we can't seem to find
any clues that would help us
shut their
operation down, devi.
[ACE]
They have to be stopped!
We have to do something!
I'll help you out!
[TAMAZO]
Tama!
You'll just get in the way.
No, I'll do better this time!
[DEVI] Master Lance,
you should take them, devi.
What for?
I'm needed back at home.
It's an emergency, devi!
[LANCE grunts]
Master Vahaton
threw out his hip
and sent me an SOS text, devi.
I need to go and
get pain-relieving patches
from Master Dafnes, devi.
[LANCE]
His hip? That's not good.
Devi. Go help.
[DEVI] Take care of
Master Lance for me, devi!
--[ACE grunts]
--[LANCE] You'll do.
Let's go.
Thanks, Your Majesty.
He gets on my nerves, tama!
Ditto!
[ACE] I guess we should
start asking around.
Door-to-door is
Investigation 101, tama!
Don't waste your time.
People here aren't
friendly to outsiders.
Oh, yeah? Watch.
Whoa! Those sure look tasty!
Have you worked at
this shop your whole life?
Yup, I took it over
when my dad retired.
Two generations of the
finest grilled seafood.
Here, kid. On the house!
Ah! Yeah, that's really good!
That guy's super-friendly, tama!
[LANCE]
Hey, you!
[gasps]
[LANCE]
Spill it.
Huh? Spill what?
Don't play dumb.
[ACE] Chill out, what do
you think you're doing?
Stopping someone
who's up to no good.
Stop being ridiculous!
[RESTAURANT OWNER A]
There he is! That's him!
[gasps]
Dine and dasher! Jeez!
Huh? Dine and dash?
Did you boys stop
that miserable thief?
Thanks a lot!
Heh.
[gasps]
[RESTAURANT OWNER A]
You're gonna wash dishes
till you've worked off your tab!
[ACE]
But how'd you know?
You can tell by looking.
Not paying
for food is a far cry
from Egg Drop trafficking!
Hey, you in the gray!
[TAMAZO]
Tama?
[LIZARD]
Hmm?
I'm sorry, don't mind him.
Get offa me!
We need to continue
our investigation!
But he's definitely a bad guy!
Just forget it!
This, my friend, is a
White Dragon's Egg Drop.
In this region,
I've hunted down
almost all of 'em.
Which means anyone who wants
one has to get it through me.
[LIZARD chuckles] And it comes
with a hefty price tag!
All my hard work is paying off.
[LIZARD chuckles]
This here is my retirement fund.
Don't even think
about stealing it.
You've really
got it all figured out,
don't you, Brother?
Better track down and
capture a rare monster yourself
if you want what I've got here.
I would if I could,
but it's not in my skill set.
Oh, by the way.
I heard there's someone
asking around town about us.
It must be someone
from the Guild.
Well, you don't say.
Guess I'll just have to
lay low after I sell these off.
[TAMAZO] If only we could
find one good lead, tama!
Hey, we just got started.
Don't give up!
Right, Lance?
You two should stay here.
I'll handle this.
[ACE]
What's with him?
[TAMAZO]
He's so frustrating, tama!
[ACE] How does Devi
deal with him all the time?
I feel sorry for the little guy.
[TAMAZO]
Tama.
[sighs]
Heya, Brother!
That's a top-rate monster
you got there.
Huh?
Have you considered selling him?
I'll pay you 3,000 krene
for him right now!
[gasps]
[ACE]
It's him.
I can't sell Tamazo!
Wait, 5,000.
No, no, I can make it ten grand!
I don't need the money.
Fine, how about trading
it for another Egg Drop?
Is there, perchance, a monster
you want more than him?
'Cause the ones
I got are rarer than rare!
[ACE] You wouldn't happen to
have a White Dragon, wouldja?
Ooh! Brother,
you sure know your stuff.
Now I don't
have the Drop with me,
so meet me here later!
[TAMAZO wails]
There we go, bud!
Tamazo, we got ourselves a lead!
You horrible brute!
You're gonna sell me off
to a stranger, tama?
No way!
I was just counting on those
star-like qualities of yours!
Well, nevermind!
[ACE chuckles]
Far too many
people in this world
have turned to darkness.
[D-GEAR rings]
Go ahead.
How are you Master?
I know you don't
like crowded places,
so I'm getting worried
about you, devi!
Well, I'm fine.
Let those two
handle the investigation!
And then all you have to do
is swoop in and save the day
like always, devi!
[beeping]
[ACE]
I think this is the place.
[TAMAZO]
Ace, look!
Hey, Brother. Hop in!
On this?
[LIZARD] I thought you
wanted to make a deal.
[ACE]
Yeah, right.
[TAMAZO] But Ace, don't
you think we should wait
for Lance, tama?
[ACE] Where's the fun in
letting that rude jerk come in
and steal all the glory?
[ACE]
Let's go.
[ACE] So, that's where
they're doing business.
[LANCE]
He wouldn't.
[LIZARD] Now, White Dragons
ain't your average monsters,
I hope you realize.
[LIZARD] Finding them
is hard enough,
and turning them
into Egg Drops
is an even more
complicated process!
Well, I'm not exactly the one
who does the capturing, but...
[ACE]
So, how do you get 'em, then?
[LIZARD]
That's a trade secret!
--Huh?
--Tama?
It's not a very fun thing
to hear about anyway.
In fact, it's better
if you don't know.
[LIZARD] All I can say is that
the poor, trusting suckers
don't even know
they're being sold off!
[ACE] So then, the monsters
are actually being conned?
[LIZARD] It's their
own fault if they fall for it.
That's how I got my hands
on this White Dragon.
[LIZARD] No disrespect, but its
power level makes your monster
look like a marshmallow!
[TAMAZO]
Tama!
[LIZARD]
Whoa!
Not so fast there, buddy.
You haven't paid me for it yet.
[ACE]
Got any others you can show me?
[LIZARD] You bet I do, kid!
Just wait right here.
[LIZARD] And don't
wander away from this spot.
A scary man will give you
a whooping if you do!
[ACE]
Let's go, partner!
This is our chance
to search the ship!
[TAMAZO]
Tama.
[CAPTAIN A] Hmm. So, this is
the White Dragon, is it?
It's almost too good to be true.
S'real all right.
I caught it myself.
[CAPTAIN A chuckles]
[LIZARD] Brother, I need to
borrow something from you
for a minute, if you don't mind.
[LOGAN]
Not right now.
[LIZARD]
Oh.
[LOGAN]
This one's called an Ouka.
These guys are pretty rare, too.
[gasps]
So, that was all your fault?!
[LIZARD yelps]
Hey! What's your problem?
[TAMAZO]
Yeah! Get him, Ace!
[ACE] My Ouka was alone
because you hunted his friends!
Who is this kid?
He's a customer I sniffed out.
He sure doesn't act like it.
This is my ship,
and I don't want any trouble,
so no funny business.
The monsters should turn
into Egg Drops because
they've accepted you
as a comrade,
not because you've tricked them!
How dare you betray
these monsters' trust
when all they want is
to be your friend!
Tch. Yeah, that's real cute,
but there's no difference
between you and me.
Either way, you're still
using the monsters in the end.
But it's not the same!
And real Dragon Callers
know that!
Now, you free all of
these monsters immediately!
Or I'll make you.
A D-Gear?
Then that must make you
the Guild Dragon Caller
I heard was snooping around.
Hey, Lizard!
[LIZARD]
Yo?
He's no customer!
He's a Guild Dragon Caller!
Do monsters really
mean that much to you?
What? Of course they do!
Well then, I have
leverage in this negotiation.
If you attack us,
I'm gonna throw
these Egg Drops in the sea.
A fate worse than death,
stuck at the bottom of the ocean
until the end of time.
[gasps]
You're a big ol' meanie, tama!
If that's what you want,
then make your move!
[ACE gulps]
It's better to
sell them off to someone
who really wants them than
to spend the rest of eternity
at the bottom of the ocean.
[LOGAN]
Wouldn't you agree?
Neither way is right!
Why don't you
just give it up already?
Hand over your D-Gear
before you regret it.
Over our dead bodies, tama!
[LOGAN]
Enough with the tough guy act,
Mr. Goody Two-Shoes
Dragon Caller would never
turn his back on
helpless monsters.
That's a good boy.
Please, sir, just
don't hurt the monsters.
Let's get rid of this!
[TAMAZO]
Tama! [grunts]
Tama!
[gasps]
[TAMAZO]
How could you be so naive, tama?
Now pipe down!
If you keep acting up,
I'll turn you into fish food!
[TAMAZO]
No, tama!
There's still so much yummy food
in this great big world
I want to try before
I get eaten, tama!
[sighs]
Take our guests to the brig.
Yeah, you got it!
Now, shall we
conclude our transaction?
You little
cretins had better
behave yourselves
now, understand?
[banging, creaking]
Looks like
the sea is getting choppy.
[CAPTAIN A]
What's that?
[CREW A]
Excuse me, Captain!
Look! There's a monster, sir!
[CAPTAIN A]
Well, get rid of it then!
[CREW A]
But it's not alone!
There's also a Dragon Caller!
There's only one?
[CREW A]
Uh. Yes, sir.
I'm guessing he's one of yours.
Uh-huh! It's Lance!
What an idiot!
[chuckles]
He's underestimating us.
All right, mates!
Show him what you're made of!
[CREW MEMBER]
Aye!
[BOTH chuckle]
[LOGAN gasps]
Captain!
Well, is it over?
[CREW B] Yes, but not
in the way you're thinking.
[CAPTAIN A]
But how?
[BOTH gasp]
[ACE]
Tamazo!
[TAMAZO]
Tama!
[CREW MEMBERS]
What are your orders?
What are you lookin' at!
Go get 'em! Go, go!
--[screams]
--[LOGAN] Hey, hold it!
[TAMAZO]
Tama, tama!
Tama!
[ACE]
Got it!
That was a mess.
Are the Egg Drops
inside that case?
You got the White Dragon's
friends back for him?
Hey, that's my...
[ACE] You mean Plesios
fetched my D-Gear?
Thanks a bunch!
[PLESIOS roars]
You punks think
you're tough, huh?
Well, I'll show you, brats.
Release!
This fight just got started!
[ACE gasps]
Heh! Looks like this
is my lucky day, kid.
Guess I don't have to worry
about losing the merchandise.
Now go.
Crush 'em, Fenrir Knight!
[WHITE DRAGON roars]
[WHITE DRAGON growls]
Hold on!
I wanna help you
save your friends!
I promise to set them free!
Now, let's fight him together!
[BABY WHITE DRAGON growls]
[ACE]
White Dragon.
Go! Release!
[LOGAN gasps]
I'm not gonna lose.
Not to someone who doesn't
care about monsters' feelings.
I refuse. You hear me?
[LOGAN yells]
[screams]
[ACE grunts]
--[ACE laughs]
--[TAMAZO] Tama!
[TAMAZO gulping, snarfing]
[GUILD DRAGON CALLER A]
Congratulations.
Thanks to the work you two did,
we were finally able to arrest
the entire Egg Drop
trafficking organization.
This case is
officially resolved.
Another great job, Lance!
Thank you,
but I didn't do it alone.
You boys really
work well together.
What do you say? You think
you wanna team up again?
I've got another contract.
[LANCE, ACE grunt]
Maybe something solo?
Agreed.
[BOTH]
Hmph.
[DAFNES]
Oh, good, Devi.
Thank you for coming.
You asked me
to keep this a secret.
Why am I here, devi?
We have something
important to discuss.
Devi.
[TAMAZO] Lance is so selfish, he
keeps on stealing our thunder!
What a troublemaker, tama!
Devi must be exhausted.
[TAMAZO] I wonder how long those
two have been together, tama?
Next time:
"The Promise in the Darkness."
In the next show,
Lance is the main character!
Tama-ma!