[NARRATOR]
The Battle Cup,
where ambitious young Dragon
Callers come to compete against
one another and determine
who's the best of the best.
It's a high-stakes tournament
where matches are fought
based on fighter classes.
They're all competing
for the glory,
as well as the Golden Egg.
The late Ancient of Light,
Master Lukes, banned Soul Brave,
an ancient Dragon
Caller technique.
However, that ban was lifted
by the current Ancient
of Light, Master Jest.
Utilizing their Soul Armor
and various monsters,
these Dragon Callers are aiming
to bring home the big win!
Ready yourselves, challengers,
for the moment of truth!
I'll wipe the floor
with that jerk!
I swear it!
Let's do it, tama!
[KROELL laughs]
Tama?!
--[ACE] Uh?
--Tama?
[KROELL laughs]
I'm afraid that's going
to be impossible.
Wha...?
[KROELL]
Before you have the opportunity
to face off against Starjohn,
you'll have to win
the finals of Class C.
However, I don't plan
to just let that happen.
And you are...?
My name is Kroell, boy,
and I'm not afraid
to get my hands dirty,
if it means winning.
[KROELL laughing]
[CROWD cheers]
Soul Brave!
A technique which had
been banned for years,
has made this tournament
one for the record books!
The contestants have really
stepped up to the challenge,
the thrill of victory pushing
them to greater heights!
Now, before we move on
to the next match,
it's time for a status report
on Classes A, B, and C!
We'll begin with Class A!
Championship contender Lance
has moved up to the finals
without breaking a sweat!
He'll be facing off
against Herriot,
the winner of the
sister-versus-sister battle!
Moving on to Class B!
Just as expected, Garnet cruised
through the early rounds
with ease, certain she had the
championship in her pocket!
But instead, she was in
for a rude awakening.
With Starjohn's fierce attack,
Garnet was injured,
and she lost the match!
That turn of events
made Starjohn
the undisputed
victor of Class B.
And last but not least,
the crowd has gone wild
for the meteoric rise of the
young stars of Class C!
[CROWD cheers]
Wow, Ace is famous!
[METAL]
A newcomer to the tournament,
and also the first
to use Soul Brave,
it's Ace from Vienna City.
He won a hard-fought battle
against his friend Charo,
and advanced to the semi-finals!
You can see how far his
training has taken him.
[METAL]
Against Ace in the finals
is another new
challenger, Kroell.
Since round one,
he's defeated his opponents
in the blink of an eye,
which means we've only seen
a handful of the cards
he has to play!
He looks tough.
I hope Ace will be all right.
[METAL]
Who will be victorious?!
Ace or Kroell?!
[METAL] The finals for
Class C will begin shortly!
You won't want to take
your eyes off of this one!
This is it, you made
it to the finals!
You've got what it takes
to win, so make us proud.
Can do.
I'm gonna take my best shot!
He'll be just fine
as long as Tamazo's in
there with him, tama!
He's in super good hands,
so you can relax, tama!
What he said!
I know, but your next
opponent is a mystery.
What's the word on
this Kroell guy?
He's been able to defeat
every opponent he's faced
in the blink of an eye while
keeping his distance.
And he... I'm not
sure how to say it.
Is there something
else I need to know?
[CHARO]
Yes.
Kroell's way of fighting
is rather unsettling.
He's very cold and dark,
like a shadow.
That could just be
the Dark attribute.
I hope that's all it is.
Something I can do for you?
You're in the finals.
That's quite an
accomplishment, Kroell.
[KROELL]
Hmph.
I've been careful not to let
anyone pull the rug out
from under me.
Guess I'm too cunning.
You haven't changed.
You're reckless, and that's
precisely why I had to give you
a failing grade in the Guild
Dragon Caller's Exam.
And from what I've seen here,
I stand behind my
decision from that day.
The way you treat your--
You know nothing!
And I'll show you
how wrong you are.
You'll see the depths
of my power.
I won't lose to a mere human.
I'm looking forward
to this fight.
I want to see the sort of power
the Ancient of Dark fears.
[CROWD cheers]
All right! Time to get the ball
rolling on the Class C final!
Ace and Kroell are
both newcomers,
but if their previous
matches are any hint,
they're gonna show us
one heckuva battle!
He's got a real nasty vibe.
You're right.
We need to stay focused.
Let's get this match started!
Hold.
Cross Fight!
[ACE]
Let's go!
Cross-On!
[METAL] It looks like both
competitors have Crossed-On!
That's not the kind of armor
I expected from Kroell .
It's actually kinda
boring, ain't it?
Come forth! Dark Dragon Knight!
Let's make the first move.
Now, show him what you've got!
Huh. How intimidating.
What happened?!
It did nothing!
Impressive! Due to Kroell's
equipped leader skill,
Dark Dragon Knight's
attack power
was just diminished by 50%!
This guy's pretty good.
Looks like it's my turn
to dish out the pain.
Release.
[ACE grunts]
Ha, ha. You're too slow.
Do it again, Black Knight!
[BLACK KNIGHT roars]
Wait, what?!
That maniac just whipped
his own monster.
Who could do something
so terrible?
[DAFNES grunts]
Oh, my.
You move too slow!
Black Knight, pick up the pace!
[ACE groaning]
Don't stop now, Black Knight!
It's time for Guard Break: Dark!
[METAL] Black Knight
has used Guard Break!
Kroell's utilization of
this skill means that
defenses have been cut
in half for Ace's team!
That's not good.
If he attacks Ace now...
This move should finish you off!
[ACE screams]
[gasps]
Ace, no!
[ACE groaning]
[KROELL grunts]
I wanted to beat
him in one shot!
You failed, Black Knight!
And now I'm done with you!
[BLACK KNIGHT groans]
He sent it back? But, why?
I have no need for
a useless monster.
What did you say?
It's your turn, Purple Demons!
That isn't hitting
him hard enough!
It's time... Purple Bomb!
[groans]
What's happening?
Goodness gracious, talk
about precarious situations.
Kroell's shaving
away Ace's guard!
Thanks to Purple Demon's
ability, Ace is in danger,
with his defenses
now down 60%!
[gasps]
Keep it up, Purple Demon!
[PURPLE DEMON 33A groans]
Hit him with all you've got!
[yells]
[ACE screams]
Ace, you still in this fight?
[ACE]
Yeah. For sure.
Persistent, aren't you?
Purple Demons,
you're even more useless
than the Black Knight was!
Now, go back!
[PURPLE DEMONS groan]
That pig.
He hurt those guys, too!
Cold-blooded.
I can't forgive that.
No way.
Hurting those monsters,
using fear to control them,
and then rejecting them?
Kroell's power is amazing!
Where have you been hiding him?
He hasn't changed
since I failed him
out of the Guild Dragon
Caller's exam.
He has a distasteful way
of controlling his
monsters using fear.
Quite inventive,
using fear to draw out
the monster's potential
to its absolute fullest.
[DAFNES] But it's an incredibly
dangerous way to fight.
You think so?
But what makes it
so dangerous, devi?
If you use fear to
control your monsters
they will become stronger,
however, they will also
become desperate.
And that's a very
risky equation.
Risk? I guess, devi.
The question is, will Ace
figure out a way to triumph?
I really don't like the
way this guy fights.
I'll stop him!
Huh. You're actually pretty
tough for a simple human.
But it's time I bring this
charade to a close.
Armor Skill!
Use Gravity World!
[TAMAZO, ACE gasping]
[CHARO gasps]
[KROELL laughing]
[groans]
Ace, no!
[CROWD chattering]
Ace...
What the heck was that?
Snap to it! Are you all right?
[ACE groaning]
It appears Kroell's activated
Hades' Soul Armor skill,
and blasted Ace
with Gravity World!
For five seconds, the
area is slowed down,
so the attacker can
line up the perfect shot!
What?! That stinks!
What a coward!
[laughs] I've toyed
with you long enough.
Now I'll defeat you in
the blink of an eye.
Pathetic humans.
It's time for you to see
what true power looks like.
Then I'm gonna have to
get my shots in now!
[ACE grunting]
Ace goes on the offensive,
but it seems he still can't
deal any damage to Kroell!
Could it be due to the fact his
Dark attack has been weakened?
Ah. What now?
[laughs] I'm going to take
my time and enjoy this.
This is the beginning
of your end!
[ACE groaning]
Be careful!
Someone stop this!
This is a nightmare!
If Ace keeps getting attacked
like this, then--
That's right!
Throw in the towel!
[GARNET]
Don't be stupid.
[BOTH gasp]
[TIGER]
Garnet!
Real Dragon Callers
never give up.
They find a way, no matter how
much damage they've taken.
That's what really
makes them great.
I guess...
Don't you worry.
Ace can turn this around.
What makes you think that?
He's an idiot.
He's too dumb to know
when to quit!
Oh, of course!
Nevermind. Try to win!
Ace! You can do it!
[CROWD cheering]
This is it!
Not this ti--!
[gasps] Tamazo!
Ha. You had to be rescued
by your monster?
You humans are even more
pathetic than I thought.
Come here, buddy.
I'll be just fine, Ace, but, can
you hear the crowd cheering?
They're rooting for you so
loudly, you can't ignore it.
Huh?
[CROWD cheering]
You're right. I won't give up!
[TAMAZO]
I have a game plan.
From All-Father Odin,
Tamazo will transform into...
Cross-On, tama!
Ohh! Awesome!
Is that...?
Oh, wow!
Odin Tamazo just Crossed-On
into a Hino Kagutsuchi Tamazo!
And that means...?
I'm not sure.
I have no idea what
those two are planning.
All right, let's
get back at him!
I'm with you.
Let's do this.
Are you really relying on your
monster's plan, little man?
That's a sign of a
weak constitution.
You're wrong!
A true Dragon Caller forges
bonds with his monsters,
and respectfully listens
to their voices!
[KROELL laughs]
You can't be serious!
Monsters are just tools to
make you better in a fight!
I won't be pulling my
punches anymore, though.
Your end approaches!
Soul Brave Hades!
That's a bunch of combos, devi!
If he lands that attack,
this fight is over.
Okay, get ready to strike!
I'm ready when you are, Tamazo!
Soul Brave Horus! Activate!
[METAL]
Ace and Kroell have both
engaged their Soul Braves
here at the end!
[ACE, TAMAZO]
Now, Yomi Wave!
What's this?
[yells]
[KROELL screaming]
What a massive turnaround
we're witnessing,
as Ace's attack hits Kroell!
This is the first time he's been
able to deal damage to him
in the entire match!
Oh, of course.
Even if his Dark
attack was halved,
he can still greatly reduce
Kroell's defenses
by using Hino Kagutsuchi.
And so he's done just that.
[KROELL]
I don't... believe it!
Tricked by a mere human!
I'm not finished yet!
Wha--?! Ace's combo is
generating multiple Cross Drops
with which to attack Kroell!
I'm bringin' this match
to an end, right now!
We'll see about that!
Good gravy!
Kroell has just materialized
some Cross Drops of his own!
Prepare yourself!
Uh? Curses.
I only have Hades.
That's the price you pay
for rejecting your monsters.
[growls] I don't care!
Hades, you should be more
than enough for this one!
Dark Hell Scythe!
Now Ace, attack him from above!
[yells]
You got it!
Huh?!
[squawks]
[CHARO laughs]
God Burning Attack!
[KROELL yells]
[gasping]
[screams]
[METAL] Using their
individual Soul Braves,
the two mega-attacks collided!
Ace's God Burning Attack has
put Kroell down for the count!
Which makes Ace the ultimate
victor in this match-up!
Which also makes him this year's
Battle Cup Class C Champion!
[CROWD cheers]
We did it!
We won, tama!
[ACE]
We won, Tamazo!
[BOTH laughing]
--You guys were amazing!
--Oh yeah! Victory!
[BOTH laughing]
[HARU]
I knew Ace could do it!
[gasps]
Master Lance,
is somethin' wrong, devi?
Nothing.
Ace was in there focusing
on his monster's voices.
He seems to become stronger
with every passing day.
Think so, devi?
[METAL] Now that Ace is
the Class C Champion,
he's earned the opportunity
to battle the respective
winners of Classes A and B
in the ultimate winner
take all combat round!
[CROWD cheers]
Ace, well done out there.
Oh, thank you very much, sir.
It was a spectacular fight,
and you lived up to the
code of the Dragon Caller.
Watching you rise through
the tournament ranks
reminded me of King.
Master Jest, you knew my father?
Naturally, King was a
great Dragon Caller,
and our rivalry pushed
me toward excellence.
And I remind you of him?
Yes, and I hope you'll grow
to be even more like him
as time goes by.
You and me both, sir.
[TAMAZO whimpers]
Tama.
I still think he's
super scary, tama.
It makes no sense.
How could a human beat me?
[DAFNES]
You still don't get it, do you?
Instead of using fear,
Ace won because of his
bond with his monsters.
If you can't understand
something so simple,
you'll never be a
true Dragon Caller.
[KROELL growls]
[KROELL]
Ace, I won't forget you,
and someday, I'm going
to make you pay!
[CHARO]
Ace!
--[ACE] Huh?
--Tama?
Hey, guys!
You finally did it, man!
Congratulations, Ace!
You're really making a name
for yourself out there.
Now nobody can
stand in your way!
It isn't over yet, boys.
--Huh?
--Uh?
You're right!
And I need to
become stronger.
The real fight hasn't started.
The true battle is still
right around the corner!
[CROWD cheers]
--[ALL] Uh?
--[TAMAZO] Tama?
Ladies and Gentlemen!
The finals for Class A will be
getting underway momentarily!
Lance versus Herriot,
and here they come now!
[CROWD cheers]
[DEVI]
Ace, White Dumpling,
don't get too cocky just
because you won
the Class C bracket, devi!
The bond between Master Lance
and me is stronger, devi!
Next time: "The Strongest
of All Dragon Callers."
Master Lance, are you
gonna do it, devi?