[NARRATOR]
For untold centuries,
there have been powerful
warriors who fought against
the various crises
that threatened our world.
They harnessed the power
of the monsters,
and forged a bond which
eased the planet's anger.
They were the Dragon Callers.
Dragon Callers are born
with the special power
to bridge the gap
between the realms
of nature, mankind,
and monsters.
When fear and hatred contaminate
the elements that surround us,
the Dragon Callers will
rise up with their monsters,
and restore balance
to our world.
[ACE]
Sonia!
You're here.
Thank you for coming.
Do you feel that?
The flow of Drops on
this island seems weird.
Almost as if it's
restless, tama!
It feels like a Drop Impact
is about to happen, tama!
That's right.
With these conditions,
it could occur at any moment.
I need your help.
I'm trying to locate
a particular monster.
What are you trying to find?
He's named Hades.
He has been called
"God of the Underworld."
[ACE]
The underworld?
He has also been known as Death.
--Tama?!
--Are you kidding me?
He sounds like a
terrifying monster!
Hades tends to attack people
by controlling monsters' minds.
So I came here to stop him.
[ACE] Then he's
somewhere on this island?
[SONIA] Yes. The Guild received
a report that he'd been sighted.
Let's split up and look for him.
Count on us, ma'am.
Wherever he is,
it's nowhere nearby.
Sonia said the monster
was known as Death.
I'm scared, tama.
What if he possesses us and
we join his undead army?
Hades, huh?
I think I've run into him
before, back in Vienna City.
But this place isn't
anything like Vienna City.
I mean, it's a
deserted island, tama!
[rumbling]
--[ACE gasps]
--Tama?
I guess it isn't deserted, tama.
It's the SDF!
I didn't know they
had a base here.
I wonder if the Guild knows
they're so close to Dragoza.
Security looks
pretty tight, tama!
[TAMAZO]
Tama!
Hey! Been a while,
White-Dumplin'!
Hiya, tama!
Of course I'd run into you here.
I could say the very same
thing about the two of you!
I was tracking down
a Drop disruption.
I knew that something
mysterious must be going on,
but I never expected that
the SDF would be involved.
Huh? What d'you mean?
It's clear to me now
that the Drop disturbance
and the SDF must be connected.
Time for us to learn how.
Okay, cool. You got a plan?
I don't think getting
inside is going to be easy.
Not an issue.
Leave it to Master Lance, devi!
He's already got everything
figured out, devi!
What's your plan?
Who goes there?
Hello. I'm a Guild
Dragon Caller.
You will let me inside.
Tama?
That's the plan you
came up with?!
Walk up and ask him?!
My, such a
straight-forward approach!
How very manly of you!
Are you kidding me?
I can't let anyone in without
the proper clearance.
[phone rings]
Nudo here.
[GUARD A] There's a problem
at the front gate, sir.
[NUDO]
I'm watching on the monitor.
Do you want me to
chase them away?
No, stand down. Open
the gate for our guests.
[GUARD A]
Sir?
[NUDO] This is a Research
and Development facility.
And I manage the various
projects we've been working on.
What kind of research
does the SDF need to do?
We study Drops
and monster biology
to better protect the people.
The more we learn, the
more efficient we'll become.
Hard to believe that's
all you're up to.
Huh. Just what are you implying?
[LANCE] You must know what's
happening
to the Drops on this island.
I'm inclined to think
you're the cause
of the Drop disturbance
in the first place.
It's no use lyin', devi!
Now spill the beans, what have
you guys really been up to?
I see.
So that's the true reason
distinguished guests
such as yourselves decided
to pay us a visit.
All right, I'll
make an exception,
and show you what
we've been working on.
Perhaps then we'll be
cleared of suspicion?
So what's this thingy?
A head-held television?
It's a prototype technology.
The visor allows the
wearer to see Drops
like a Dragon Caller would.
That's awesome!
Then people like Mom and Haru
could see the
beauty of the Drops!
That's right, and
in the near future.
[TAMAZO]
I can't see anything, tama.
I told you,
it's under development.
People believe in what they
can see with their own eyes.
This technology will make
the populace more aware
of the true danger
of Drop disturbances.
Does this put your mind
at ease? I hope so.
We are very proud
of our research,
and we at the SDF
will continue striving
to safeguard the
future of this world.
A device that would make
everyone able to see Drops.
That seems like a
worthwhile project.
I guess the SDF is
pretty useful, tama!
Yup!
We only saw one of the projects.
He's hiding something.
So what should we do?
I'm not sure.
Devi?
Tama?
A monster! They caged him!
Lance, I didn't know
you would be here.
Yeah! We bumped into each other!
We weren't able to locate Hades,
but we stumbled
across an SDF base.
There's an SDF base?
That's right,
and I'm pretty sure
there's a correlation
between them and the
recent Drop disturbance.
I discovered something as well.
There are no monsters left on
this island. They've vanished.
What?
The SDF must be to blame.
We even saw a monster
they captured.
The monsters utilize Drops
as a food-like energy source.
Without monsters, the flow
of Drops is disturbed
and becomes imbalanced,
which leads to Drop Impacts.
How can they not understand
something so simple?
They do. It's intentional.
[gasps]
Wait, what are you saying?
They're causing
the Drop disturbance,
and they're doing
it purposefully?
Devi.
Where are you going?
[LANCE
You have to ask?
Devi? Devi.
He's going to stop them alone?
[alarm blaring]
[OPERATOR A] Systems have
detected a Drop Impact, sir.
It's located in the
Northwest forest.
We're picking up a rogue
energy signature now.
Sir! It's a monster!
Deploy all troops!
Don't let that monster
come near this base!
[beeping]
[OPERATOR C] Adjutant Nudo.
Cameras show an intruder, sir!
[DEVI]
Devi.
[roars]
They have all these poor
monsters locked up!
What a buncha meanies, devi!
Time to set you all free, devi.
[NUDO] I'm afraid I have
to stop you there.
Devi?
Sometimes you don't
get what you want.
Each of those monsters
is a test subject
vital to the furthering
of our research.
[DEVI]
Devi?
I demand that you
release them immediately.
Or I'll be forced to
report this to the Guild.
[NUDO]
Hm.
And what can the
Guild do about it?
[LANCE] Are you crazy?
You're a Dragonoid!
Why would you side
with the humans?
You take a great deal of pride
in being a Dragonoid, don't you?
It's almost as if you
consider our entire species
to be infallible.
I was much like you
when I was younger.
But I have watched
the Dragonoids' power
wane over the years.
This planet is in
imminent danger.
Relying on old values
won't save us.
Let's look at things critically.
The Dragonoids' racial powers
aren't helping any of us.
The Guild is well on its way
towards collapse from within.
What was that?
[NUDO]
The humans aren't our enemies.
You need to determine
who the true foes are.
You don't want someone to
pull the rug out from under you.
Hey, Lance!
What is it?
I came to help you
rescue the monsters!
Button pushing time, tama!
[roars]
Opening all the cages, tama!
Now's our chance! Let's move it!
Take aim! Don't let any
of the monsters escape!
The monsters haven't
done anything to them!
Savages.
Halt! Who are you?
[SONIA] It's not enough that
you used the monsters,
now you have to cause them pain?
I'll take on the lot of you!
[yells]
How dare you!
[ACE]
No, Sonia! Stop!
[roars]
Look out, Ace!
[yelps]
Sonia, no!
Ready? Engage!
[ACE]
Sonia!
I'm okay. Just dazed.
Hades is using his mind
control on that Leviathan.
Now it's your turn.
I know you've got what
it takes to stop him.
Time to stand and fight, tama!
I'll go take down Hades.
You guys handle the Leviathan.
Let's go, Devi!
[DEVI]
Devi
Armor Drop, devi!
[LANCE]
Cross-On!
Release!
Tama, tama, tama, tama,
tama! Cross-On, tama!
Awesome!
[ACE]
Let's do this! White Dragon!
Ouka! Dark Dragon Knight!
Our attacks are no good!
[roars]
Are you recording everything?
[OPERATOR D]
Yes, sir.
Monitors are also
capturing Drop activity
thanks to our camera sensors.
Perfect.
We're paying a steep price,
but for significant returns.
Here he comes, Ace!
Blue Troll!
Your place is the
underworld. Return!
Now go. Aoyaiba!
Okay! Let's do this, Tamazo!
Gungnir!
This is your chance, Ace!
[yells]
He's back to normal.
He became an Egg Drop.
Looks like we did it, tama.
[ACE]
Mh-hm.
[ACE gasps]
[HADES] You cannot defeat me.
I will always return.
Hades. What a
horrifying monster.
The SDF must have somehow
brought him to this island.
He shouldn't be here.
[KING]
Hello there.
Leave this place.
You humans are disruptive.
No, just listen.
I am not your enemy.
I came because I heard a
Dragon Caller lived out here.
[SONIA]
What do you want?
I came because our
planet is in peril,
and I need your
help to protect it.
I don't work with humans.
Now get out!
So you plan to stay in
this forest all by yourself?
You can only achieve
so much on your own.
[yells]
[gasps]
Don't let your talents go
to waste. That'd be a shame.
There's a place in the Guild
for people with your abilities.
Humans and monsters
can co-exist,
but it all starts with a choice.
So what's yours?
How are you feeling?
You had me worried.
[SONIA]
Did you carry me in here?
I did.
It's been so long since
I last had a dream.
I saw an old friend this time.
Easy, now. You're still injured.
It's just a scratch,
nothing serious.
I'll be just fine.
I'm the child of a union between
a Dragonoid and a monster.
Hybrid offspring aren't very
common in either world.
[ACE]
What?
The monster blood in my
veins gives me power,
but I can't live a normal life.
It's my curse, so I chose
to hide away in the forest
and live amongst the monsters.
But why'd you live with them?
Because I'm able to understand
the monsters' intentions.
Mostly. But I didn't know
how to use my power.
All I could really do was hate
those who ruined the forest.
Then I met someone who
put me on the path
to becoming a Dragon Caller.
But if I had never met him,
I might've used my powers
incorrectly, hurt somebody,
or even worse.
But that isn't you.
He saved me, and now you've
rescued me as well.
[chuckles]
What? Uh. Come on.
I didn't do that much!
Looks like the Drop
disturbance has settled down.
Hi, Sonia! Are you
feeling better, tama?
I am.
[TAMAZO]
That makes me happy, tama!
Good thing she's
all right, devi!
Let's go.
The entire balance of Drops
is maintained because
of the monsters.
Humans and monsters will have
to find a way to co-exist,
and the Dragon Callers are our
best hope to bridge that divide.
You're right.
There's still so much about
this job I have to learn.
But I...
I know one thing with
absolute certainty.
Whether you're a human or a
monster doesn't matter to me.
This is everyone's planet, and
we all have to fight for it!
Yes, that's right, Ace.
What do you say?
Want to fight for it together?
[ACE]
Yes.
[TAMAZO] Star John, a
Dragon Caller so powerful
that gods serve him!
But his identity
remains a secret.
He's powerful, but no
one knows him, tama?
Sounds fishy, tama.
Next time! "The One
Protected by Gods."
God only knows who
he really is, tama.