[CHARO giggles]
[ACE]
What's up?
[CHARO] I'm still so
excited that I finally got
my Soul Armor!
[CHARO] And one as
awesome as Fortoytops!
[CHARO]
Do you wanna see it?
Because I could Cross-On now.
Eh? No, thanks.
I've already seen it,
like, 12 times.
[CHARO] It's almost time
for the Battle Cup!
I really want to get some more
powerful Egg Drops by then.
[TIGER yells]
[ACE]
Tiger?
[CHARO]
What're you doing?
[TIGER] Check it out,
I found something awesome!
[BOTH]
Huh?
[CHARO]
Is it a monster?
[TIGER]
Hmph!
Unicorn Bug!
What now?
What's so great about it?
Does it turn into an Egg Drop?
Of course not!
Don't be silly, dude.
It's just for fun.
Fun only.
Unicorn beetles are cool!
Uh, neat.
So, why are we
in this forest again?
For the insect collecting.
That's what you
do in the forest!
I've never seen one of these
guys this big before.
[TAMAZO]
Tama?
[TIGER]
Unicorn beetle's horn strike!
[CHARO] Tiger always makes
whatever he's doing fun.
He doesn't have
a care in the world.
I know.
[TIGER]
Horn strike!
--Hah! He's comin' to get you!
--[TAMAZO] Stop it, tama!
[WOMAN]
Now, what do we have here?
Huh...?
[ROSE] I heard a noise, and I
came to see what was going on.
[gasps]
No way! Rose?
[TAMAZO]
Tama?
Long time no see.
Tiger.
[ACE] So Rose, you and
Tiger have been friends
since you were children?
[ROSE]
Yes, but I have to say.
I never expected to bump
into you in this forest!
Guess what.
I've become a
Guild Dragon Caller, too!
That was your dream!
Good for you!
Yeah, thanks.
So is that why
you came to the forest?
Are you trying to find a
Red Carbuncle, like I am?
Yes?
[TAMAZO]
Tiger!
I found another
unicorn beetle, tama!
It's even bigger than
the one you found earlier!
Unicorn beetle?
Ah! No, no, no, no!
Don't listen to that egghead!
I came out here to find
the Red Crabapple thing,
just like you said!
But you said it
was about insect collecti--
[yelps]
You haven't changed,
have you, Tiger?
Well, old friend.
What do you say
to a little contest to see
which of us can find the
Red Carbuncle first?
[TIGER]
Huh...?
[ROSE]
All right!
And they're off!
Wait! I'm not ready!
Doesn't seem like she's
changed much, either.
So, is your friend a
Guild Dragon Caller, too?
Her? Yeah.
Back in the day,
we used to train together.
You'd trained before we met you?
Yup, I was with Rose
when I found this little guy.
[pants]
Hah! Looks like I win!
I guess so, but running's
the only thing your good at.
[TIGER]
C'mon, just let me enjoy this--
Oh, no! Agdralls!
And they're blocking off
our escape route!
Escape route?
Why would we need to get away?
They're bound to become
our allies when we show them
the iron-strength of
our fighting spirit!
Now, Agdrall!
I'll allow you to join my team!
I did it!
Become my ally! Agdrall!
[AGDRALL growls]
[TIGER grunts]
So then, is that a no?
[AGDRALL growls, grunts]
What exactly was your plan here?
[AGDRALL yipping]
Please, Agdrall.
I really want you
to be part of my team!
[ROSE sighs]
[AGDRALL growls]
[TIGER sighs]
Become my ally.
I'm begging you!
Hurry up! Tiger!
Please, just think it over!
[gasps]
[ROSE sighs]
I am so beyond
psyched right now!
Welcome aboard, Agdrall dude!
Mmmwah!
I almost pity
the poor thing,
having an ally who's
so dorkishly obnoxious!
No one will blame you
if you run away.
Don't even joke about that!
[ROSE giggles]
[BOTH laugh]
Hey, Rose! Let's work
together to become
the top Dragon Callers!
[gasps, sighs]
We're so good,
we'll make it look easy.
At least you will!
Become my ally.
I'm begging you!
Please, just think it over!
[ROSE growls]
[TIGER]
You're leaving Geyser?
[ROSE]
Yes.
Cool. I'll come with you.
[ROSE]
I'm going alone.
--[TIGER gasps] Alone?
--Without you.
But why, Rose?
It'll be a lot more fun if we
keep traveling together!
[ROSE] We can't get stronger if
we're focused on having fun.
[gasps, sighs]
What has gotten into you?
[TIGER] I thought
that we promised
to get stronger together?
[ROSE]
That's why...
Our promise...
[ROSE] Let's get stronger, and
then we'll be strong together
at the top.
[TIGER]
Rose!
[CHARO] Here's the page
on the Red Carbuncle.
It's a monster
with fire attribute.
[ACE]
Aw! It's adorable!
Awesome! I'm gonna prove
that I'm worthy by finding
this Red Carbuncle
before Rose does!
[ACE]
Tiger!
[CHARO]
Don't run off without us!
Come out!
Red Carbuncle!
Something tells me it
isn't going to be that easy
Who's this dude?
This monster evolves
into a Red Carbuncle.
It's called a Red Krull.
But, he was pretty easy
to find, tama!
Yeah, and it looks
like The Monster Book
essentially agrees with you.
Aww, now there's three of 'em!
Hey, little Red Krullie-woolies!
Do you guys wanna play?
[TIGER]
Huh...?
[CHARO "However,
Red Krulls travel in packs,
which makes them stronger,
and therefore,
more difficult for a
neophyte to obtain."
[TIGER] I wish you'd gotten to
that part a little bit sooner.
[TAMAZO]
Tama.
[TIGER]
That stinking varmint!
[TAMAZO] His cuteness
was pretty deceiving, tama.
[CHARO] It just goes
to show, you should never
judge a book by its cover.
[ACE] We've gotta catch one
before he calls his friends in.
[CHARO]
There's one!
[GROUP screams]
[TAMAZO]
Red Krulls are like roaches.
If you see one, there are
probably five more, tama.
I won't stop.
I need to get that Egg Drop!
I think I know what to do.
When we track down a Red Krull,
the three of us will gather up
as many Fire Drops
as we possibly can...
...and hit him
with an ambush combo!
So like, a mass attack?
That could work!
Great idea, Charo!
[CHARO chuckles]
[TAMAZO]
Tama.
He's up ahead, tama!
[TIGER]
I'm gonna get you this time!
[RED KRULL A squeaks]
[yells]
[TAMAZO]
Hurry, tama!
Before he gets a chance to
summon his friends, tama!
No way!
There aren't enough Drops!
I can help!
Let's always go
for the top together!
Go, Tiger!
Here it comes,
you little red menace!
My signature final attack:
The Cross-Counter Punch!
[grunts]
[TIGER]
I did it!
You're gonna make a great
addition to my team!
That was great!
And when did you come up
with that special attack
you just did?
It was so cool!
Oh, that?
I was just in the moment, and in
a fit of passion it came to me.
[TAMAZO]
In other words, you winged it.
Uh...
Well, that figures!
Randomly yelling out a string of
cool-sounding words isn't quite
the same as having a real
special attack, now is it?
[TIGER]
Pipe down!
[TAMAZO] It's so dorky,
it actually fits you, tama.
[CHARO]
Big time!
[TIGER]
Stop being so mean, you guys!
[GROUP laughs]
[TIGER]
Come on!
Rose!
[gasps]
[TIGER] Say hello to my
freshly-caught Red Krull!
[ROSE]
Yeah, so what?
I thought the whole reason
you came here was to find
a Red Carbuncle!
Uh! Yeah, of course,
but he's gonna evolve
into a Red Carbuncle one day.
And when will that be?
Dunno.
Oh! Right!
I bet Charo would know!
Yeah! He was that
little short dude I was with.
He might be just a kid, but he
knows a ton about monsters!
[sighs]
I met my friends in Geyser
and started traveling
with them. It's the best!
And the other guy, Ace,
can generate Drops
from far away.
The two of them are
some of the nicest guys.
You'd like 'em, too, Rose!
Tiger. You really
haven't changed at all.
Huh?
You've made no progress.
I have so done stuff!
One: I've joined the Guild, and
two: I have my own Soul Armor.
I'm not the same guy
as I was before!
So then... you're
still going for the top?
Of course!
Very well. Let's have a battle!
[gasps]
[ROSE] Put your money
where your mouth is.
Time to test out this
stronger version of you.
[TIGER]
If you want.
I'll oblige ya,
but ya might regret it.
[ROSE]
Show me what you've got!
[TIGER]
Let's do this!
Cross-On time!
[TIGER] Forget the
concept of impossible!
I'm here to make
my dreams come true!
All right! Let's rock, partners!
Release!
[TIGER]
How's that?
It's pretty cool, I know.
[TIGER] I make Entetsu's
Soul Armor look good!
I told you I'd gotten stronger!
[ROSE]
That's it?
Huh?
[growls]
Now!
Release!
[gasps]
[ROSE] This is the same
Agdrall I caught the day
we were together.
[ROSE] He's already
evolved into Flare Drall.
[TIGER gasps]
[ROSE]
Just watch!
[growls]
[AGDRALL growls]
[FLARE DRALL. roars]
[AGDRALL yelps]
No, Agdrall!
If that was all you've got,
then I'm disappointed.
[TIGER growls]
Release, Krull!
It's cute, but Red Krulls
are nothing without their pack!
[RED KRULL A screeches]
Just like you, Tiger.
[ROSE]
So you've joined the Guild,
and gotten yourself
a Soul Armor as well.
You look and sound like
you're a real tough customer.
But no.
What a shame.
I really had my hopes up that
you had changed somehow.
You haven't.
[gasps]
[ROSE sighs]
[ACE] So, did Rose already
head out for the next town?
--Yeah...
--Then that begs the question:
Where should
we head to next?
[TAMAZO] I want to go
somewhere that has
really tasty food, tama!
I think we should go
where we can find rare monsters!
I need to get
some stronger monsters
fighting for me!
What do you think, Ace?
Where would you like to go?
[ACE]
I dunno.
[ROSE] Red Krulls are nothing
without their pack!
Just like you, Tiger.
[TIGER]
When I found my Red Krull.
[TIGER] Charo thought of
the plan to catch him,
and Ace provided
the Drops.
But what did I do to earn this?
I really had my hopes up
that you had changed somehow.
You haven't.
[TIGER]
I was wrong.
[CHARO]
Tiger.
Hello? Tiger!
[gasps]
Mountain or ocean:
where would you rather we go?
A hot spring resort
in the mountains
sounds pretty nice, doesn't it?
Melon splitting at the beach!
I want to feed Beetles
some watermelon.
--[TAMAZO laughs]
--[TIGER] Yeah...
[ACE]
What's wrong, Tiger?
[TIGER]
[ACE] I don't know,
you just seem down.
No, I'm totally fine.
You're such a cutie, tama!
Hey, Tiger!
Let's put out the syrup trap
again to catch more beetles
so that he has a couple
of friends, tama!
[TIGER]
Okay.
[BOTH]
Uh...
[CHARO]
Why don't we go here?
They have hot springs!
[ACE]
Sure, that sounds good!
What do you think?
--Tiger?
--[TAMAZO] Tama?
[ACE]
So, what's your vote?
The hot springs?
The beach?
Tiger. What's the
matter with you?
You've been acting really
strange since last night.
Are you coming down with a cold?
[TAMAZO] I hope it wasn't
food poisoning, tama.
[BOTH]
Hmm...
No, I... I'll go on my own.
Ah! You'll go on your own?
What does that mean?
[TIGER] From here on,
I've got to make my own way.
[BOTH gasp]
I've decided!
What're you saying?!
If we're all going to go
the same place,
then why can't we
go there together?
[TIGER]
We may share direction,
but that doesn't mean the path
you choose is right for me.
[TIGER] 'Cause I have
my own path to walk!
That's why... it's time
I headed out on my own!
Okay.
Are you serious?!
How is it okay, Ace?!
Don't you want
Tiger to be with us?!
This is Tiger's decision, Charo.
But it's not!
[TIGER]
Thank you, Ace.
Well, I'm against it!
I think Tiger should stay with
us and continue having fun!
We've had great adventures!
Don't you want to share more
of them with your friends?
I can't get stronger
by just having fun.
That's not right!
What you're saying
doesn't make any sense!
You can have fun
and still keep getting stronger.
What part of having a little fun
means you can't be strong?
I'm not saying having
fun is a bad thing.
But after our time
traveling together,
I rely on you too much.
And I wanna be able
to do things on my own.
If I'm not goofing around,
I can focus more on training.
That's the only way
to become the strongest
and most fun version of myself.
I get it.
You sound
like a real know-it-all.
Charo!
Talking like that,
trying to sound like
you're so mature.
Like I'm a kid,
so I wouldn't understand.
Does talking down
to me like that make you feel
like a big-shot?
[ACE]
Charo!
[CHARO] Why are you changing
who you are all of a sudden?
Was the other you an act?
Are you a liar?
[ACE]
That's not how it is!
[TIGER sighs]
My bad! Don't be so upset!
I was only trying to yank your
chain a bit, you know?
And I think my little mop-top
friend here fell for it!
To be honest, I just did
this whole mature speech thing
to show off to Rose.
Basically, she mocked
me about hanging out
with my buddies all the
time, and so I said to her:
"Whatever!
Tiger will always be
a lone wolf, lady!"
Or somethin' like that.
Uh...
I need to tell Rose
I said all those things
to impress her, but she's
all the way back in the city.
Might take awhile,
you know how slow I can be.
I'll catch up with you guys.
No need to wait up, okay?
I'll be--
Oh, hey there, Tamazo.
[TAMAZO grunts]
Ouch, that hurts.
[TAMAZO whimpers]
Tama!
Tamazo!
Okay, well, I'll see ya soon.
All right. See you later.
[TIGER]
Land!
Bubbling over with
passion, I'm aiming for the top!
Geyser's fiery man about town.
They call me Tiger!
Don't worry about it,
little buddy!
Either way, you've got
guts and heart!
That's what counts.
Sounds like a plan.
Let's give it
everything we've got!
[CHARO whimpers]
Well then, I think I will!
It's time to go for the top!
[CHARO sobs]
[TIGER]
You guys!
Go for the top!
I'll see you there!
Heh.
[CHARO, ACE]
Yeah!
[ACE]
A lot of things have happened
since I first came to Dragoza.
Some were scary, some were fun,
and some of them
were a little sad.
[ACE] There are so many
things I'd like to say, but...
Next time:
"E-mail from Ace."
Why are e-mails
so hard to write?