[NARRATOR]
For untold centuries,
there have been powerful
warriors who fought against
the various crises that
threatened our world.
They harnessed
the power of the monsters
and forged a bond which
eased the planet's anger.
They were the Dragon Callers.
[NARRATOR] Dragon Callers
are born with the special power
to bridge the gap between
the realms of nature.
Mankind and monsters.
When fear and hatred contaminate
the elements that surround us...
...the Dragon Callers will
rise up with their monsters
and restore balance
to our world.
Cross-On!
Wow! What was that?
[roars]
[CHAOS DEVIL DRAGON roars]
Whoa, it's an adult
Chaos Devil Dragon!
He looks even cooler in person!
[sirens blaring]
Your orders?
We stop him here.
Prepare the Anti-Drop Cannons!
[CHAOS DEVIL DRAGON growls]
Come, monster allies.
Unleash your might on my enemy
and bring him down!
Release! [yells]
[roars]
[roaring]
Wrath of the Black Dragon--
Activate, now!
[roars]
Maybe this will help you
cool off a little!
[yelling]
[roars]
We did it!
Sir! It stopped moving.
It what?
I'm truly sorry
I had to rough you up.
I hope you can understand. This
city's no place for a dragon.
[CHAOS DEVIL DRAGON growls]
[LANCE] Go on.
Go back to where you belong.
[CHAOS DEVIL DRAGON growls]
This is it! Anti-Drop Cannon!
Fire!
[CHAOS DEVIL DRAGON roaring]
[gasps]
[roars]
[growls]
Those morons!
[SOLDIER C screaming]
Pull back, men! Retreat! Go, go!
[CHAOS DEVIL DRAGON roars]
[growls] Dragon Lord Zaerog.
Please, give me your energy!
[yells]
[CHAOS DEVIL DRAGON growls]
Man, our weapons are
nothing compared to that!
He's amazing.
No way! One Dragon Caller was
able to bring that giant down!
Run, you idiot!
Devi.
--[CHAOS DEVIL DRAGON growls]
--[ACE gasps]
Move it, kid! He's attacking!
[gasps]
Now get out of the way!
[ACE grunts]
He needs more power-
Those things block the Drops...
[VOICE] Can you feel
the Drops, Tama?
[gasps]
[VOICE]
Open your heart, Tama!
Open my heart?
[VOICE]
You can do it, Ace!
[ACE]
I can?
But there aren't any more
Drops down here.
[ACE]
But the sky...
The wind... the clouds...
[grunts softly]
[ACE]
I've gotta try!
Again?
Master Lance!
[LANCE] Hmph. So be it.
I'll use your Drops.
[DEVI]
Six combos, Devi!
[CHAOS DEVIL DRAGON roars]
[gasps]
[VOICE]
Ta...ma!
[ACE gasps]
Stop that!
--Could ya cut it out?!
--I'm so happy!
Gimme a break!
[LANCE]
What is it? Devi?
Is he the same as you?
Devi isn't nearly
that round, Master.
What do we do now, Devi?
That's an excellent question.
First, a bite to eat,
then a good night's rest.
The Drop balance is
back to its normal level.
Impact dissipated!
I guess we did it, Commander!
We did nothing.
[FEMALE REPORTER A]
Oh, Commander, sir!
Do you have a victory speech
you'd like to share with us?
[MALE REPORTER A]
Is the city safe?
Can we all relax now?
The egg hatched, Wise One.
King's son and the hatchling
are together now.
Their fates have
been interwoven.
I feel the time is
drawing ever nearer.
[TV ANNOUNCER A] The Drop
Impact has dissipated
to acceptable levels,
thanks to the heroic efforts
of the valiant SDF!
We're just glad that no
civilians were harmed
during the operation.
We heard a rumor
that a Dragon Caller
was on scene as well.
Is there any truth to that?
That was not the case.
This victory was due to the
SDF's elite training
and equipment!
[TV ANNOUNCER A] And in
other news,
the Vienna City Dragon Museum
will host a live mega-event
this afternoon: The Battle
of the Dragon Callers!
It's a rare opportunity for us
to see the fabled fighters...
Bye, Mom, I'm off!
[LENA]
Hold it right there, Mister!
Aren't you forgetting something?
[TAMAZO squeals]
[ACE sighs]
Come on, Drops!
Tama?
Why aren't the Drops
popping up?
You must put your
whole heart into it.
[ACE gasps]
So how do I do that, huh?
[SONIA]
That's for you to figure out.
Are you another Dragon Caller?
I might be.
Do you want to learn more?
Tama?
[SONIA] Perhaps you should take
a tour of the Dragon Museum.
[ACE]
Hmm...
[TAMAZO]
♪ Tama, tama! ♪
♪ Tama-tama-tama! ♪
♪ Tama-tama-tama-tama! ♪
So, like, what's your deal?
You look like the monster
he had with him.
Tamaa!
[ACE]
Hmm...
[grunting]
Hey! That was my
lunch, egg-head!
[BUS DRIVER] Next stop,
Dragon Museum Station.
Dragon Museum Station,
next stop.
[beeping]
[GARNET] Hey, Lance? The event's
about to start, y'know!
You are coming, right?
I might.
[GARNET sighs] Look, you
better not blow this off, okay?
[sighs softly] Dragon Callers
aren't here to entertain.
[GARNET] Hang on!
Are you even listening?
I can smell the egg, Devi!
[GARNET]
Hey, so? Hello? Lance?
[LANCE sighs]
Okay, I'll be right there.
[GARNET]
What? So you are coming?
[METAL] Welcome, one and all, to
the Vienna City Dragon Museum!
The mighty Dragon Callers!
Using the powers
in elemental Drops,
they fight alongside
their monster allies!
Dragon Caller Battles are how
we find the best of the best!
And the best duelers
become world famous!
But there's more to them
than battling each other!
They fight rogue monsters
in order to dissipate
Drop Impact and maintain
the balance of the elements!
That is the Dragon Caller's
true destiny!
--[GIRLS squeal]
--What the...?
[TAMAZO]
Hmm?
What kind of species is he?
I can't find him in the
monster book. How strange!
What? Really?
Oh! Sorry about that!
I wasn't trying to intrude on
your business, Mister...?
[ACE]
Uh. You can call me Ace.
And my name is Charo.
Hi! So, Ace, did you come down
to see the Dragon Callers, too?
We get to see 'em?
--Yup! And then--
--[HARU] Ace?
What're you doing here?
Does it matter?
You came down to see the
Dragon Callers, too, didn't you?
I wouldn't miss it
for the whole world!
They say Lance
is going to be here!
A thousand monsters
couldn't keep me away!
She's right! It's not
every day you get to
meet actual, authentic
Dragon Callers!
How many chances
like this do you get?
[METAL] And without
further ado, let's begin!
--[GIRLS gasping]
--Outta my way!
--Come on!
--Aah!
[TAMAZO yells]
What is it?
Guess I was wrong about you.
I thought you were
a total show-off.
[sighs softly]
The TV said that nobody
in town got hurt.
And you saved my life.
I just did what any worthwhile
Dragon Caller would've done.
Well, thank you. But the TV
gave all the credit to the SDF.
That's fine. Dragon Callers
aren't here to entertain.
[DEVI]
De-vi-vi.
[TAMAZO]
Tama,, tama-tama...
[LANCE] Anyway, think you can
show me what you did yesterday?
[ACE]
Huh?
Oh!
Do it now.
Ahh...!
[grunting]
[LANCE]
Guess it wasn't you.
Hey, wait up! I can do it!
I just have to put my whole
heart into it or--something.
Ahh!
[LANCE]
Hmph. I'm taking him with me.
Huh?!
Tama?
We came here, all the way from
Dragoza Island just to find him.
Tama!
[ACE]
Whoa. Hold on a second!
[LANCE]
Let's go.
[DEVI]
Hey, you took my seat, Devi!
What's with him?
[METAL panting]
Excuse me, have you
seen Lance anywhere?!
[METAL]
Oh! Oh, come on!
[GIRLS murmuring]
I can't believe I to get to
meet real Dragon Callers!
Hello. I hate to be
the bearer of bad news,
but due to unforeseen
circumstances--
which I assume were of
an emergency nature.--
Mister Lance won't
be joining us!
--Are you kiddin' me?!
--What?!
Talk about a rip off!
[GIRLS yelling]
[GARNET]
Hello, Vienna City!
Sorry for the wait, everyone!
It's me, the super-cute
Dragon Caller!
Garnet the Great!
Uh...
[groans]
Wow! Yes! It's Miss Garnet!
She's super awesome!
Thank you! You're sweet!
Okay, then! It's show time!
You ready?
--[BOYS yelling]
--[CHARO laughs]
[DEVI]
After a hard day's work,
nothing's tastier than having
lunch while airborne, Devi!
I'm a nice guy, so you
can share mine. Devi-vi?
He's gone, Master!
He's what?
[DEVI screams]
Dine and dash!
[LANCE growls]
[ACE sighs] Wonder what that
egg thing even came here for.
[TAMAZO]
I came to see you, Ace!
Little guy even knew my name.
[yelps]
Where'd you come from?!
Tama!
I thought you went with Lance!
Won't they be worried?
I stick with you, Tama!
With me?
Of course! Your lunch
was by far the tastiest!
[groans softly]
Hey, least you're honest.
Stinking jerks!
They all came to see Lance, huh?
[grunts]
[GARNET squeals]
You saw that?!
Then I have no choice.
[CHARO]
No! I didn't see anything!
[CHARO yelps]
Swear it! Swear you
won't tell anyone!
--[CHARO] Yes! Fine!
--[GARNET] Good.
[CHARO sighs]
Miss Garnet, please!
I have a request!
Make me your pupil!
Huh?
I want to be a Dragon Caller
one day, like you!
I've dreamt of it
as long as I can remember!
Okay, but can you
create Drops?
Um. I haven't been able
to create any... yet.
Tough news, kid.
Sounds hopeless.
[gasps] I'll try! But I'm not
really sure where to begin!
Watch me!
So can you see 'em?
It's something that I've always
been able to do, you know.
I guess it's what
you'd call a gift,
and you just haven't got it!
No, but, what about my dream?
[GARNET] I think you give up on
that now, rather than later.
And now we're done here.
That's a pretty rude
thing to say.
[CHARO]
Ace.
Oh, yeah?
Who are you, hotshot?
Do you have any idea who I am?
--No clue.
--Tama.
Can't believe I set
myself up for that burn!
[ACE grunts]
Uh. What the...
Well now! You see 'em!
How 'bout a little duel, so you
never forget my name again?
Bring it on, tough guy!
What are you talking about?
A Dragon Caller's Battle, duh!
No, that's a terrible idea!
I'll lend you a hand, Tama!
He just spoke?
I better get an extra
tasty lunch if I win!
You just had one!
What is he?
He kinda looks like Devi.
Man, people who use those
fat-egg type monsters
are totally stuck-up poseurs!
I'm gonna tear you
into little pieces.
Then use those pieces
to spell out my name.
Release.
[DRAGON squeals]
Ta-da! Now, show me
what you've got!
[ACE gasps softly]
What's wrong?
Are you scared of me?
Ace! Just line up
the gold Drops, Tama!
Line 'em up?
Wait, so you can
see Drops, Ace?
You've gotta line 'em up
in groups of three or more!
[ACE]
Like this?
Tama! I'm all revved up!
One combo? That's baby stuff!
Keep working on it for
another million years,
and maybe you'll have
a shot at me then.
[GARNET]
Where did those come from?!
[GARNET growls]
Never mind.
Tama?
You can't walk away!
I'm overflowing with
power over here!
Oh, hush! As if I'd ever take
this pipsqueak seriously!
[ACE]
Hey, Garnet!
[GARNET] At least you know
my name now, don't you?
I'll let it slide this time.
Uh, wha...?
Wow, Ace! You lined up
the Drops on your first try!
You're a natural!
Oh, yeah? You mean it?
Yeah, and...
...I wanted to say thanks
for sticking up for me.
Sure, kid! No prob!
[BOTH chuckle]
[GARNET growls]
What was that?!
[SONIA]
Garnet.
Hey Sonia! Why're you here?
No way... Not him!
Why did you stop your
battle with him?
That's simple--because
if two Dragon Callers
fought it out in the courtyard,
we would've made quite a mess,
wouldn't we?
Good thinking, Garnet.
Thank you.
[LENA]
But the egg he found,
it was the same kind
of egg King had.
I thought it was
only my imagination,
but no--it looks like Ace has
too much of his father in him.
[ANGINE]
Remember to breathe, Lena.
Why don't you send
the boy to us?
There's a lot we can
teach him on Dragoza Island.
[ACE gasps] Where'd the
egg-head run off to?
We've made contact
with the monster!
Tama?
[TAMAZO]
I hatched, Tama!
Now that I'm outta my shell,
I'm going to try all
the yummy food I can find!
Wait, this place
doesn't look right-- Ace!
Save me from these weirdos!
Next Episode:
"Operation Tamazo Rescue."
I wonder what sort of grub
they'll feed me here, Tama.