[NARRATOR]
The Battle Cup,
where ambitious young Dragon
Callers come to compete against
one another and determine
who's the best of the best.
It's a high-stakes tournament
where matches are fought
based on fighter classes.
They're all competing
for the glory,
as well as the Golden Egg.
The late Ancient of Light,
Master Lukes, banned Soul Brave,
an ancient Dragon
Caller technique.
However, that ban was lifted
by the current Ancient
of Light, Master Jest.
Utilizing their Soul Armor
and various monsters,
these Dragon Callers are aiming
to bring home the big win!
Ready yourselves, challengers,
for the moment of truth!
[CROWD cheers]
I never thought the final
round would be against you.
Yeah, what Master Lance said!
I can't believe you
made it this far.
We'll see if you have
real power, devi!
This isn't gonna go down
like the Guild exam.
I'm not a rookie Caller
tryin' to pass a test!
I came here to win!
Without further ado,
let's get this final Battle
Cup match started!
Cross Fight!
[squawks]
[ACE]
Cross-On!
You're up...
...Tamazo!
Oh, yeah, you got it!
Gungnir! Ha!
Armor Skill, Eye of Wadjet!
It's time, you guys!
Time to end this.
[yelling]
[screams]
[LANCE]
What now?
Are you ready to give up?
As long as I can fight,
I'll never quit!
Mirage Blade attack!
[roars]
[ACE screaming]
[METAL] Aoyaiba's skill
strikes Ace hard!
'Cause I have you
fighting at my side!
So I know... I can... win!
[yells]
That's a surprise.
[CROWD cheers]
Get ready, Lance.
[yells]
[gasps]
I stopped it!
[LANCE gasps]
[ACE yells]
It's our turn now, tama!
[ACE]
Yeah! [yells]
[ACE yells]
[ACE grunting]
There you go!
Let him have it, tama!
Where does he get off, treating
Master Lance like that, devi?!
Ace is on his feet?
That kid's somethin'.
But how? He was so
weak a minute ago!
And now he's rocking
things full throttle!
It's from Tamazo,
that's the real power.
[groans]
[ACE yells]
Quite the reversal.
This is awesome!
Careful...
[CROWD cheers]
[MONSTERS roar]
I feel the power flowing
through me.
Ace! Attack him now!
All right, let's go!
[PLESIOS roars]
[BOTH yell]
[CROWD cheers]
Close, but need more power!
[LANCE grunts]
Here it comes!
[TAMAZO]
Push it back, tama!
[ACE]
Go!
[yells]
[ACE]
I can do this!
I can take Lance on,
head-to-head!
Ace, you're strong.
No matter.
Get ready!
[LANCE grunts]
[gasps]
I'm not gonna lose this!
[TAMAZO]
Ace, keep attacking, tama!
You've gotta go for it!
[ACE]
Yeah!
[yells]
It seems his Soul Armor
has reached its limit.
Maybe it's due to fighting
a foe of Lance's strength?
[JEST chuckles]
Yes, Lance is strong.
No, it's... not that.
[gasps]
[DAFNES]
Could it be...?
[CROWD cheers]
All right, Ace! Keep swinging!
I can't believe he's
actually giving Lance
a run for his money!
And it's all thanks
to Mister Tamazo.
He might really win
this thing after all.
Come on, Ace! You can do it!
You're lookin' good
out there, Ace!
Give it everything you've got,
and see it through to the end!
You both look totally
cool! Keep it up!
Oh, Ace.
[yelps]
[groans]
[ACE groaning]
Ace! No!
I'm fine.
Tamazo, let's go!
[TAMAZO]
You got it, tama!
[HORUS squawks]
[LANCE]
Hmph. Well, then...
He's laughing, devi.
It's been far too long
since I had to get serious.
[ACE grunts]
[ACE yelling]
[LANCE grunts]
[WOMAN 37A]
They're incredible!
[MAN 37A] I can't even
keep up with them!
[MAN 37B]
This fight's remarkable!
[WOMAN 37B]
It's too fast to see anything!
[crash]
[JEST] I never imagined Ace
would become this strong,
much less so quickly.
But it's more
favorable this way.
His strength will spur
Lance on to new heights.
[yells]
[ACE groans]
[WOMAN 37A]
Oh! His Soul Armor!
[WOMAN 37B gasps]
[MAN 37C]
Is he all right?
[TAMAZO]
Ace! Are you okay?
I'm just fine.
Let's go, Tamazo!
[TAMAZO]
With pleasure, tama!
[TIGER] Hey, does Ace's Soul
Armor look kinda weird?
Well, according to my datapad,
an update is required.
[ALL groan]
[CROWD cheering]
That armor's degraded to
the point of being useless.
I'm surprised he's holding up.
The kid has heart.
Come on...
[MAN 37A]
Did you see that?
[WOMAN 37A]
Keep it up!
[WOMAN 37B]
Lance is so strong!
[ACE]
I can track Lance's every move.
And I feel so light!
I can't imagine losing!
Oh, yeah! Let him have it!
Crush him! Stick and move, tama!
Right!
[gasps]
[ACE growls]
[yells]
Not quite.
I still need more power!
[MAN 37A gasps]
[WOMAN 37A]
His Soul Armor keeps fading!
[MAN 37D] It isn't supposed
to do that, right?
Are you sure this is normal?
Should I worry?
Just look into his eyes.
[gasps]
Go Ace!
You can do it!
So headstrong, devi.
His Soul Armor is
pretty much worthless
after Master Lance's
attack flurry.
Just give it up already, devi!
Devi, you've got it all wrong.
Devi?
That is from his power.
Devi?!
Okay!
Let's attack him
with White Dragon
and Leviathan
simultaneously, tama!
No way.
That's not enough!
I need everyone attacking
at the same time.
[OUKA growls]
[DARK DRAGON KNIGHT roars]
[WHITE DRAGON roars]
[LEVIATHAN roars]
Cross-On, tama! Hi-yah! Ha!
Oh! Awesome!
Let's send a full force
assault Lance's way!
[MONSTERS roar]
[yells] It's on now.
Here's God Burning Attack!
[gasps]
Huh? Wait, what?
[TAMAZO]
Uh!
[LANCE grunts]
Whoa! His Soul Armor seems to
have completely degenerated!
[MAN 37B]
What's he gonna do now?
[CHARO gasping]
Then that means his
defenses are gone, right?
Is Ace gonna be okay?
Of course he isn't
gonna be okay!
If Ace takes a big hit
without functional Armor...
Oh, no.
Things are looking pretty rough.
Stop, Ace! You've done great!
You really impressed me!
But please quit
before you get hurt!
[WOMAN 37A]
So is that it?
[MAN 37A] You can't beat Lance
with your Armor like that!
What now?
What's going on?
He didn't notice, devi?
So it would seem.
I know Horus is still on
my side. I feel his power.
I'm still in this fight!
You're sure?
Everyone! Let's go!
[MONSTERS roar]
It has to be.
You've grown stronger.
All right, then.
[ACE grunting]
[ACE groans]
This is all too much!
Why doesn't someone stop them?!
Master Vahaton.
Should we intervene?
Hm...
Let them continue.
I don't think that Ace
is ready to give up yet.
[JEST]
Become stronger, son of King...
...so that Lance might.
[ACE grunts]
[yells]
You know, I'm thankful.
It's been too long since I had
a match that challenged me.
Thanks, Lance.
I still plan on
beating you anyway.
I'll win and surpass you.
But first, I need more power.
Come on!
[grunts]
[LANCE grunts]
[yells]
I need more!
Even more power!
I'll be stronger than Lance,
than anyone!
Stronger.
I'll be the strongest
Caller there's ever been!
[gasps]
Incredible.
[squawks]
Could it be? Did Ace really...
That's it!
What's going on, Master Vahaton?
His Soul Armor is reacting that
way because it cannot keep up
with the sheer magnitude
of Ace's power.
Wha...?
So it wasn't because
Lance was destroying it?
That's right, the combination
of his Tamadra's power
with Horus and the
use of Soul Brave
has increased Ace's
strength exponentially.
[DAFNES] Simply put, this
Soul Armor reached its limit.
Dude, what is
happening with him?
It's strange.
I've never seen
anything like it!
[gasps] No way!
Horus, are you going to
answer to Ace's strength?
"Answer Ace's strength"?
You mean--?
[JEST chuckles]
[ACE screams]
[HORUS squawks]
Ace, your Soul Armor
just evolved!
[CROWD cheers]
Wow! Ladies and gents,
I can barely believe it!
It appears Ace's
Soul Armor has evolved
in the middle of their battle!
That's... That's amazing!
--[TIGER] Way to go! Awesome!
--[GARNET] Way to go! Great job!
You're amazing, Ace!
[BOTH gasping]
[ACE]
Lance...
Ready to kick things up a notch?
[LANCE growls]
Ace!
[LANCE]
Tch. Idiot.
You don't have enough control
to handle that kind of power!
Next time: "The Final Battle."
I'm putting an end
to this right now!