Hurry, we gotta move!
Is it a Drop Impact?!
[ACE grunts]
Huh?
Huh...?
[CAMPERS murmuring]
[ACE gasps]
[ACE] I could've sworn
that was a Drop Impact.
[CHARO]
Yeah, we're lucky it wasn't.
[ACE gasps]
Wow! Charo, look!
[CHARO chuckles]
It's a hot air balloon!
It uses fire to
float across the sky!
[ACE]
Cool...
[ACE] I didn't know what to
expect when we got to Geyser,
but it's a really
interesting place!
Tamazo. What do you
think you're doing?
So toasty warm! Come on in,
guys, the water's fine!
Perfect, Tama!
Geyser's become one of
the top tourist destinations
because they have natural
hot springs all over the place.
[TAMAZO] We can even make
soft-boiled eggs, Tama!
They're even tastier when
you share with your friends!
Not a care in the world.
Today's another chance
to reach for the top!
[yells]
That's the one drawback.
Eccentric types flock
to places like this.
Too true.
[beeping]
What's up, Garnet?
[GARNET]
Where are you guys?!
Oh, uh...
We went to the Fire City.
[GARNET]
Get over here ASAP!
Get over where ASAP?
A part-time job?
[GARNET] I'm supposed to be
doing a live concert here.
But we're short-staffed,
which is where the two of
you work into the equation.
But we just got to town,
and there's still
a ton of sightseeing stuff
we kinda wanted to do.
Totally. I didn't come all
the way to the Fire City
just to work some
dumb pop gig.
What are you talking about?
I mean, you should be thanking
me for giving you a shot
in the entertainment biz!
Oh, wow. Thanks. Uh.
Everything's set, Miss.
We're on standby-mode!
Thank you!
Now get to work! Move!
What a letdown!
Roped into working for her.
Hey. Garnet's no Lance, clearly.
If he threw a concert,
just imagine what kind
of crowd would show up!
This should be a piece of cake!
You're right!
Garnet's sorta mediocre as both
a celebrity and as a
Dragon Caller, in all honesty.
It isn't very fair to
compare her to Lance, though.
Seriously, she's nowhere
near his skill level.
[gasps]
[GARNET growls softly]
Did you hear that?!
--[ACE whimpers]
--Because we were joking!
You know us...
Break a leg...
Oh, man. I can't believe
she didn't kill us!
She might.
They didn't have to say
all that stuff behind my back.
I already knew.
[GARNET]
Is that a Drop Impact?!
[CEO]
You're late!
Huh?
We have work to do,
young lady.
Oh? Is that right?
We've got publicity
to cultivate!
I've already lined up a meet and
greet before your concert
at one of the local hot springs.
A meet and greet at
the hot springs?
[STAFF B]
What a small audience.
[STAFF A] Well. You know how
it is: Garnet is no Lance.
Tell me about it.
If Lance did shows,
he'd need more than some
local banquet room, right?
Small potatoes. [laughs]
So whaddaya wanna do for lunch?
[STAFF B]
I dunno, hoagies?
What's the saying?
"Jack-of-all-trades,
master of none."
I need to focus on
one or the other.
Huh?
[ACE whimpers]
Why don't you go
apologize to her first?
Why do I have to go first?
[GARNET]
You two!
The last thing I need is
somebody coming along
and disturbing my private time!
Especially when those somebodies
are two pathetic losers
who failed the Guild exam!
[BOTH gulp]
Just so you know,
I passed on my first try.
[BOTH grunt]
I bet you'll flunk
your next exam, too.
Your faces just scream failure.
[CHARO whimpers]
You keep hitting
below the belt,
and I'm not gonna put up
with it anymore!
You're ready to pull your
D-Gear out because of this?
You child.
A Dragon Caller should never
point their D-Gear at people.
I thought even a fool
like you would've known that.
[gasps]
No wonder you didn't pass
that last Guild exam.
You. Can't. Win. You. Nerds.
You're so mean...
Yeah? At least we're
not begging for fans!
[VOICE]
Stop it!
[ALL gasp]
Huh?
Who's that?
[VOICE]
Jump!
Land!
Bubbling over with passion,
I'm aiming for the top!
Geyser's fiery man about town.
They call me Tiger!
[ACE, CHARO]
Huh...?
Okay. Back off, boys.
If you guys are trying
to stalk Garnet,
then I'm gonna
make you regret it!
Why don't you two find
something better to do
than scaring a poor,
fragile little girl!
Does she look scared?!
And besides, I wouldn't
refer to Garnet as "fragile."
As a top Guild Dragon Caller
of the future, I'll stop you!
Do what now?
Not now, but later.
I don't really understand
what you're trying to tell us.
I haven't exactly passed
the Guild exam up to this point.
But wait-- I'll become a
top Guild Dragon Caller!
Then you'll know my name!
So you failed the exam, too?
Oh, yeah! That last exam
totally kicked my butt!
[laughs]
That's strange.
You don't seem upset.
Failing the test only
means that I have
the opportunity to take
it again someday!
You're certainly optimistic!
[STAFF A] Miss Garnet, ma'am?
It's time for tech rehearsal!
Okay! Bye-bye, boys.
Wish me luck!
[giggles]
[TIGER chuckles]
[GARNET] Unbelievable!
Surrounded by simpletons.
[TIGER] Hold up!
Where are you going?!
Aren't you gonna battle me?!
[TAMAZO]
Ace! Charo!
The soft-boiled eggs are
ready and looking good!
Tama?
Two, three, four, five,
six, seven, eight, nine, ten!
I win! Yeah!
--In your FACE!
--[ACE] It was a massacre.
It's pretty immature
to cheer like that
after defeating a child.
Looks like I'm top dog
around here! Yeah!
[TAMAZO]
Whatcha doing, Tama?
You boiled up some
tasty eggs, Tamazo.
Yum! Thanks.
So, Tiger, do you call
the Fire City your hometown?
Sure do. Born and raised
right here, in Geyser.
What about you two? Is this
your first time visiting?
[CHARO]
Mm-hmm.
We've got a ton of geothermal
hot-springs around here.
The food's delicious
and the people are warm.
It's a heckuva place!
You should stick around!
You're right.
The locals are friendly.
I'm glad we met. Each of
us is an unwilling member
of the Fraternity of
Guild-Exam-Failers, after all.
Y'know, I never really thought
about it that way, little buddy.
It's nothing to be proud of.
[gasps]
I just remembered!
We were supposed to secure
the building for Miss Garnet's
meet and greet thingy!
She's going to kill us!
I can't believe we forgot!
A Meet and Greet?
Tama!
There's bound to be
some fans there already,
even if it is just
to meet Garnet!
We'd better
get a move on, Ace!
Yeah!
--[TIGER chuckles]
--[TAMAZO] Tama...
Nobody came.
--[CEO laughs nervously]
--This is humiliating.
So, there was a bit of
a communication breakdown
with the printing service,
and they put the wrong place
and time on all the flyers.
"Meet singing sensation
Garnet in Hell"?
This had better be a joke!
It was supposed to say
"Meet Garnet in
Hell Valley Hot Springs."
But this makes it sound
like you're awaiting
their arrival in the depths
of the underworld. [laughs]
Hello? Oh, hi!
I'm glad you called!
What's that? Hello?
[CEO] How strange.
Bad reception? Can you hear me?
[GARNET groans]
No one's coming? Seriously?
[gasps]
[ELDERLY MAN] Excuse me.
I'm trying to get here.
Oh, uh... Take this
exit, go straight,
and then make your way
towards the right.
Follow the pathway
and you should find it.
Thank you, miss.
[REPORTER]
In further news,
Guild Dragon Caller Lance
has once again
dissipated the Drop
Impact in the region.
The city is safe, and
peace has been restored.
All thanks to the
heroic efforts of Lance.
I can't keep
going on like this...
[sighs]
Maybe I should quit...
[yells]
[yelling continues]
[pants]
[ACE]
Huh...?
[TAMAZO]
Tama...?
Oh no! It looks
like we completely
missed the meet and greet!
[sobs]
You must really like
Miss Garnet a lot, huh, Tiger?
--Huh?!
--[TAMAZO] Tama...?
It's not anything
like that at all!
Why would you assume
something so ridiculous?!
But I thought Garnet's
show was the entire reason
you came here
in the first place.
You kidding me?!
I only care about
becoming a Dragon Caller!
Everything else is
merely a distraction!
I don't have time for girls.
I've gotta try to keep
my head in the game!
Besides... A pop star?
No, thank you.
I'm not even remotely
interested in that. Hah!
He's pretty easy to read.
Uh-huh.
[TAMAZO] Tama-tama-tama!
He's scary, Tama!
[gasps] I think it's just about
time for Garnet's concert
to get started.
Yeah?
[explosion]
[ACE]
What the--?
Maybe it's another
volcanic eruption?
I mean, Geyser
is the Fire City.
[screaming]
[gasping]
[RED FLAME MALLET TROLL
growling]
What is this?!
Those red trolls are
going on a rampage!
Bad news, Tama!
What're we gonna do?!
We don't have much choice.
Yeah! Let's take
care of business!
[RED FLAME MALLET TROLL A
growls]
[RED TROLL A, B yell]
[ALL grunting]
They're so full of rage.
They're becoming reckless, Tama!
Stand back, guys!
Uh-- Garnet?
What are you doing out here?
Why don't you leave
these monsters to us?
Your concert's supposed
to start soon, isn't it?
It's fine. I've decided to quit.
[BOYS]
What?
I won't get any better
if I'm juggling both.
Can't be great like Lance.
[gasps]
You can't compare your
best to someone else's.
Huh?
I mean, sure, your
singing is mediocre.
And so is your dancing.
And you really
stink as an actor.
Looks-wise, you're a seven.
No, in the celebrity
world, you'd be a six.
Or maybe even a five.
Wow. Thanks.
Doesn't matter! 'Cause your
set blew me away that day!
I'll never forget it. It was
the very same day I failed
the Guild Exam for, like,
the tenth time.
What? You've failed that much?
That's gotta be
pretty discouraging.
No way, I don't
care 'bout that.
[TAMAZO] Tama?
You really didn't care?
I wondered about why I
was unable to pass the exam.
I figured it was because
I didn't have any Soul Armor.
So I constructed
a suit of my own!
There's no other set
like it in the whole world!
Made by--ahem--me.
Wait. It's hand-made?
Yeah, that's right.
I got myself all psyched up,
put my armor on at home,
then I hit the road,
ready to take the exam.
You wore it at home?
Never heard of
anyone doing that before.
You were way too
excited, Tama.
I won't forget.
Oh, man! Check out
that guy's Soul Armor!
Nice DIY project!
That's just pathetic.
[TIGER] I thought about
giving up on my dream
of becoming a Guild
Dragon Caller.
[TAMAZO] He can be quiet
and reflective, Tama.
[TIGER] That's when
I first saw Garnet.
She had just started
her career as a singer.
At the time, Garnet
didn't have any fancy outfits.
She was up onstage singing and
dancing in her ugly clothes.
How lame!
[giggling]
[TIGER] She didn't care
how other people saw her.
The only thing she brought to
the table was her passion.
But that was all she needed.
And when I realized that,
my life changed.
I swore that day to
never give up on anything
I loved just because
someone might laugh at me.
I realized I didn't have
to be ashamed of the things
that made me happy!
Garnet's spark
set my heart aflame!
[yells]
I love you!
People can laugh,
but it's never gonna stop me
from reaching for
my personal best!
It's dumb to give up because
you compare yourself to others!
The only thing that matters
is that you strive
to reach your top!
[CROWD] Garnet! Garnet!
Garnet! Garnet! Garnet!
Go to your fans,
they're waiting for you.
[ALL gasp]
[RED TROLLS grunting]
I'll let you Exam-Failers deal
with these guys,
I've got a show!
Like they say, three heads
are better than one!
[RED TROLLS growl]
The little ones are
called Red Trolls!
The big one is a
Red Flame Mallet Troll!
Both monsters fall under
the fire attribute!
Let's go, Tamazo!
You can count on me, Tama!
Cross-On!
[yells]
Ha!
Cross-On, Tama!
Oh! Awesome!
[RED TROLLS growl]
[ACE] Good. This place
is full of Fire Drops.
Ouka. Release!
[OUKA barks]
[RED FLAME MALLET TROLL A
growls]
[OUKA barks]
--[ACE gasps]
--[OUKA growls]
[growls]
I got this! Now, release!
Go, Agdrall! Let's rock!
[TIGER]
Cross-On!
Ta-da!
[ACE]
Huh?!
You're kidding me!
Is that the hand-made Soul Armor
he was talking about?!
He just drew on some cardboard.
Maybe he used a technique
to actually make
that Soul Armor awesome!
[RED FLAME MALLET TROLL A
growls]
[gasps]
[yelps]
Nope. I guess it was
just normal cardboard.
[RED TROLLS growl]
Okay, Ace and Tiger!
You have to attack in tandem!
[ACE]
Mm-hmm!
[TIGER groans]
I'm gonna go for the top!
[RED TROLLS growl]
[yells]
[OUKA barks]
[AGDRALL grunts]
[RED TROLLS growl]
[barks]
[yells]
[RED TROLLS growl]
[RED FLAME MALLET TROLL A
growls]
[yelling]
Great work, guys!
[gasps]
[RED FLAME MALLET TROLL A
growls]
[AGDRALL whimpers]
[RED FLAME MALLET TROLL A
grunts]
[OUKA yelps]
--Oh, no!
--Ouka!
It's no good.
This one's just too strong!
[GARNET]
♪ Just be yourself... ♪
[RED FLAME MALLET TROLL A
growls]
This is bad! If he rampages
through the concert,
people are gonna get hurt!
We better go!
[CROWD cheers]
This next number is brand new!
Why don't we kick
things up a notch?!
[cheering continues]
That's not good!
Garnet!
[BOTH gasp]
♪ I'm unstoppable
'cause I do it all! ♪
♪ I won't chicken out
I'm always ready to roll ♪
♪ Who cares if
I fight or fall? ♪
♪ I got moves that'll
take down any foe ♪
♪ So, get ready for
my miracle combo! ♪
[BACKUP SINGERS]
Yay! Yay! Yay, yay, yay, yay!
[GARNET] ♪ There's those who
can come and join in the fun ♪
♪ The special dungeon
is waiting for us ♪
♪ Combos make rhythyms make
all charging up ♪
♪ It's time to sing,
it's time to play ♪
♪ You can like singing too ♪
♪ So loud and proud,
let me hear you ♪
♪ Making our voices heard ♪
♪ We're not alone
when we harmonize ♪
♪ La. La. La la la la. ♪
♪ La. La. ♪
♪ La la la la. ♪
♪ La. La. La la la la. ♪
♪ La. La. ♪
♪ La la la la. ♪
[CROWD cheering]
[CEO]
Hey, great show today!
I mean, that was some
absolutely captivating
entertainment, Garnet!
A crowd response like that makes
it all worthwhile, right? Hm?
Oh, we got another job offer
that I'm waiting
to pull the trigger on.
The stage is smaller
than here, in full disclosure.
And I'm not really sure
how many people will show up.
Whaddaya think? I could call
back and turn them down.
[GARNET grunts] Of course
I'll play the show.
I'm never going to give up
on being a Dragon Caller
or a performer!
Promise. I'm always
going to shoot for the top!
[TIGER] I achieved top-notch
cheering for her today!
Garnet's performance was
really on point, huh?
She was superb, tama!
She really was!
Which was almost as surprising
to me as when Tiger
openly confessed
his love for Garnet
while she was
standing right there!
[TIGER]
Huh? No, I did not!
Well, first you went:
[yells]
[laughs]
No way! I think you
most likely misheard me.
Eh? Huh?
Score!
It seems fate has led
our party to a hot spring!
Let's say we take a dip?
Whoa. Like, right now?
Yeah! Uh, why not?
Let's see. "Why not"?
It would be foolish to
miss the chance for a bath
when it's right in front of you!
Hygiene's important if
you wanna reach the top!
Banzai!
[TIGER screams]
It's just water!
Cold, frigid water!
[screams]
Freezing!
I can honestly say that's
the stupidest person
I've met so far.
[TIGER]
Why is the water cold?!
It was supposed
to be hot, but it wasn't!
[CHARO] Hot springs
are always refreshing.
And they're apparently supposed
to do wonders for your skin!
But suddenly, the hot
spring has gone cold!
Next time!
"Ancient of Fire, Eldora!"
If we don't fix it,
no more soft-boiled eggs!