[NARRATOR]
For untold centuries,
there have been powerful
warriors who fought against
the various crises that
threatened our world.
They harnessed
the power of the monsters
and forged a bond which
eased the planet's anger.
They were... the Dragon Callers.
[NARRATOR] Dragon Callers
are born with the special power
to bridge the gap between
the realms of nature,
mankind, and monsters.
When fear and hatred contaminate
the elements that surround us,
the Dragon Callers will rise up
with their monsters...
...and restore balance
to our world.
[ACE] This is
my hometown, Vienna City.
Not long ago, our city was
the site of a Drop Impact.
[ACE] This is a Guild
Dragon Caller named Lance.
And even though he's
responsible for saving our town,
I think he's also pretty rude.
[TAMAZO]
Taa...ma!
[ACE]
And this little guy is Tamazo.
He's a weirdo monster
who loves people food
that I hatched from a
strange egg I found.
Don't give up yet, Tama!
[ACE] From the moment
Tamazo and I met,
my power as a Dragon Caller
was awakened.
[ACE]
Cross-On!
That armor makes you
look ultra-cool!
[ACE chuckles]
[panting]
[OUKA panting]
Tama!
[ACE grunts]
[OUKA grunts]
Tama!
[giggles] Tama!
[TAMAZO squeals]
There!
[barks]
[MYSTIC DARK KNIGHT growls]
Ouka!
[OUKA roars]
[grunts]
[MYSTIC DARK KNIGHT yells]
[gasps]
[MYSTIC DARK KNIGHT]
Huh? Huh?
Here we... go!
[yells]
[OUKA roars]
[MYSTIC DARK KNIGHT yells]
[OUKA barks]
[MYSTIC DARK KNIGHT groans]
[MYSTIC DARK KNIGHT sighs]
You did it, Ace! Wow,
a Mystic Dark Knight's Egg Drop!
[ACE] Hello, Mystic Dark Knight!
Welcome aboard!
Look who else found one, Tama!
[CHARO]
So what is it?
[BADDIE squeaks]
[gasps]
That monster isn't
worth our time!
Jya-ha! As if I
would ever lose to you!
Why are you competing
with me, you weirdo?
Don't forget to set
the egg in your D-Gear.
Oh! Right!
[ACE]
Mystic Dark Knight! Release!
[laughs]
Cross-On!
[yells]
Tamazo!
Tama!
[yells]
Kabuki-style Cross-On!
[laughs]
Yo! So. Awesome!
Cool! I like it!
Oh my! Tama!
[laughs]
[gasps] Nice! I really like
the "easy-going" pose!
Yeah? You mean it?
[CHARO]
This group shot is fantastic!
I feel like I'm
stronger with more
monster allies backing me up.
You are stronger,
no doubt about it!
With the Mystic Dark Knight
on your side,
you've really leveled up!
And to have Soul Armor
on top of that?
I bet you're unstoppable!
Whoa, unstoppable?
[CHARO]
You're a real big-shot now!
Evil-doers, make way for me!
[CHARO]
Awesome!
I'm amped up!
Now I wanna battle something!
Hey! Let's spar!
[TAMAZO]
Ace!
Uh.
Oh, wow, guys!
Can you smell that
delicious aroma, Tama?!
Hey, get back here!
[LANCE grunts]
[SONIA] The Drop concentration
is growing higher.
Yes. We're due for
an Impact any time.
It's going to be big.
I'll call the twins.
There's no need.
I can handle it alone.
[DEVI] Just leave it in
Master Lance's capable hands.
He won't let you down, Devi!
He's pushing away help
and acting like a maverick.
But the tree that refuses
to bend may just break.
[ACE, CHARO panting]
This looks yummy, Tama!
Looks like we found
a mapple tree!
[OUKA, BADDIE groaning]
Sorry, guys, that's not a Drop.
[OUKA grunts]
[laughs]
Hey, Ace, this tree
has a sign on it.
[TAMAZO] The sign says it's
Ace's mapple tree, Tama!
[gasps]
[ACE] So I just have to
plant one and it'll grow?
[KING] Hmm... The soil
around here isn't right for it.
Oh. 'Kay...
Don't worry. I'll find the
perfect spot to plant it.
[gasps]
[whimpers]
[CHARO]
Hmm? Is something wrong?
[TAMAZO]
Tama?
[ACE]
No. It's nothing.
Hey, ping-pong ball!
Yeah, I'm talkin' to you, Devi!
Who do you think you are,
lunch stealer?!
[blows air]
[DEVI]
Okay, that's it!
[ACE]
Hey! C'mon, take it easy!
Aren't you Lance's monster?
Then your boss can't
be too far away.
Better believe it, Devi.
The water city Crocus is
Master Lance's hometown, Devi.
Oh, I didn't know that.
[chuckles]
Look! I became
a Dragon Caller, too!
And I helped!
I don't think
he's buying it.
So now, whenever the next
Drop Impact comes down,
I can help out!
[LANCE]
Don't fool yourself.
Listen well. Don't go sticking
your nose in our business.
Huh?
[DEVI chuckles]
What a total jerk.
"Don't go sticking your nose
in our super-serious
business," Tama.
It went something
kinda like that.
What an arrogant show-off.
[VAHATON sighs]
Maybe I didn't do as good a job
at raising him as I'd hoped.
Wait, what do you mean?
Well, Master Vahaton took
the boy in and raised him, Ace.
Lance is an orphan.
[gasping]
[VAHATON] But that youngster
can be such a pain.
I want to spend more quality
time together as a family.
But he never stops by to visit,
and I haven't laid
eyes on him in ages.
Not even a g-LANCE,
get it? O-ho!
Jokes like that're probably
why he won't come visit, Tama.
[VAHATON gasps]
[laughs] My King did the same
thing when he was Lance's age.
[VAHATON]
By the way,
I've sensed a great disturbance
recently in the Drop Balance.
Perhaps the planet
needs to tell us something
and this is how
it draws our attention.
[VAHATON]
That might be.
But we can expect a Drop Impact
of epic proportions soon.
[ANGENE chuckles]
[VAHATON] Last time it got this
bad, King had to save us all!
I couldn't believe he
dissipated a Drop Impact
of that magnitude single-handed!
My father didn't need any help?
Your dad's awesome!
I wonder if I can
ever be like him?
I believe that you can, Ace!
[VAHATON]
King was one of the all-time
greatest Dragon Callers.
As long as you keep
your mind on your training,
you'll open up your
own path in no time!
Besides, the Dragon
Caller's true essence--
[ALL yelp]
What's that?
[TAMAZO]
Tama, tama, tama! [squealing]
A new Drop Impact...
[VAHATON]
Could it possibly...?
[VAHATON] It is. This is
just like that day.
No, this Drop Impact
seems even more severe!
What in the world is happening?
[gasps]
[tower chimes,
sirens blaring]
[DRAGON CALLER A]
Master! It hit Linus Prairie.
[VAHATON] Summon the
other Dragon Callers.
--I can help!
--Ace?
[VAHATON] You three! Stay
inside this house, understand?!
[ACE, CHARO whimper]
Best to leave things to
the Guild Dragon Callers
and stay out of their way.
[ACE, CHARO groan]
[BOTH chuckle]
Fine.
I'm a Dragon Caller,
too, you know.
This is the perfect chance
to see some rare monsters!
Hey, it's go time!
[TAMAZO groans]
You can't be serious, Tama.
'Cause I'm already so snug!
--[ACE] Come on!
--[TAMAZO] Tama!
[CROWD murmuring]
[MAN A] Now! Close the gate!
Monsters are coming!
[YELLOW EVILS snarling]
[CHARO] Those are
called Yellow Evils!
I'm not sure
what the big one is.
[ACE]
No!
Whoa, hold on!
Where are you going?!
[wind howling]
[ACE]
The mapple tree is in danger!
What are you doing?!
Wait for us!
[ACE panting]
[TAMAZO]
Tama!
[DONNY]
Hey! Stop! It's dangerous!
Well, you can't say
I didn't warn you.
[ACE] Back then,
all I could do was watch.
[ACE]
But things are different now.
[MORIGANNON growls]
--[gasps]
--[YELLOW EVILS growling]
Hoo, boy. I'd better head home.
[GARNET] My, my! You're supposed
to be a Dragon Caller?
I thought it was your duty
to stay and protect
the people of this city!
Come on, cut me some slack!
Nobody in their right mind
would dare to pick a fight
with so many monsters!
[HERRIOT] All right,
scumbags! Bring it on!
[DONNY]
You see?!
[YELLOW EVIL A screeches]
Watch out!
--[HERRIOT grunts]
--[YELLOW EVIL A squawks]
Did she just punch it?!
It's child's play.
Don't need my monsters for this!
[MORGAN] Oh, sister, dear!
You're always so violent.
[DONNY gasps]
Now then Mister
Amateur Dragon Caller.
Would you please move aside?
What's that?
You talking to me?
[squeals]
[YELLOW EVILS screech]
[MORGAN giggles]
[YELLOW EVILS screeching]
[yells]
[YELLOW EVIL G grunts]
She's incredible!
[HERRIOT] Looks like we
cleared 'em outta this area.
Wow! You're Ms. Morgan
and Ms. Herriot!
The powerful
Dragon Caller of Light,
and the Dragon Caller of Dark!
You're famous! And Twins!
Yup!
We're famous. And beautiful!
And I'm their Dragon Caller
Celebrity protégé!
Can we have one moment
that's not about you?!
Anyway, where are
Ace and Charo?
I was looking forward to
introducing those clowns
to my masters.
Oh, they both went that
way a little while ago.
[GARNET gasps]
[DONNY]
Hey, I tried to warn 'em!
What were they thinking?!
Those morons!
Are you serious?
That kid's pretty courageous!
I swear, gutsy boys
make my knees weak!
[groans] I know these guys,
and they're not gutsy.
They're just
unbelievably idiotic.
[MORIGANNON growls]
I won't let any harm
come to this mapple tree!
Ouka and Mystic Dark
Knight, get ready!
[yells]
Release!
Cross-On!
[MORIGANNON growls]
Big Green is a Morigannon!
Use Ouka's fire to
exploit his weakness!
'Kay, I got it!
Old Dragon Knight's
Code, activate!
[roars]
[yells]
[OUKA roars]
[ACE yells]
[MORIGANNON growls]
Stop him!
[roars]
[MORIGANNON growls]
[TAMAZO]
You did it, Ace!
That was so incredible!
That monster looked real tough,
but you stomped him!
I had no idea I was capable
of wielding so much power!
Now that the biggest monster
has been defeated,
the Drop Impact should
dissipate any minute now.
Great work, today!
--[rumbling]
--[CHARO gasps]
--[ACE, CHARO gasp]
--[TAMAZO] Tama!
[BALROG growls]
[CHARO]
He's huge!
I understand.
The Drop Impact should go away
if I defeat him, right?
This monster's way
out of your league! Huh?!
I was able to beat that
other one all by myself!
No! He's too strong!
[ACE yells]
[BALROG roars]
[ANGENE]
Hmm...? Well, that's a shock.
Those kids sure are quiet.
Oh, no. Ace's plate--
it's cracked.
Ouka! Inferno Blast!
[OUKA roars]
[BALROG roars]
[ACE grunts, gasps]
[OUKA growls]
Tama!
Cross-On, Tama!
Awesome!
Ugh, enough with the
theatrics, already!
Help me, Tamazo!
Tama? Behold! Gungnir!
That is not good.
[BALROG roars]
It's up to me!
[yells]
[ACE groans]
[BALROG roars]
He put in five combos
and it did nothing!
Ace doesn't have
enough monsters to win...
[gasps]
Oh no! He's about
to use his Mirage Flare!
Ace, you have to run!
[BALROG roars]
[gasps]
[OUKA barks]
No... He's down!
And to have Soul Armor
on top of that?!
I bet you're unstoppable!
Whoa, unstoppable?
[CHARO]
You're a real big-shot now!
Evil-doers, make way for me!
[CHARO]
Awesome!
I'm amped up!
It's my fault...
I made him think that...
[TAMAZO whines]
Tama...
[ACE groans]
Just hang in there...
--[CHARO gasps]
--[ACE yells]
Oh no, Ace! [gasps]
Can you hear me?! Ace!
[gasps]
All these Drops. How?
This just proves that
Ace was trying his hardest.
[CHARO whimpers]
I see every color of Drop,
and I can't do anything to help!
[BALROG roars]
[gasps]
[CHARO]
Huh...?
[LANCE] Idiots. I told you
to stay out of my business.
You need to recognize
your own limitations.
You should've fought him
closer to the city.
You both have a lot to learn.
[CHARO whimpers]
[LANCE]
Stay back.
[DEVI]
Hah! Cross-On, Devi!
[DEVI yells]
Yeah, Devivebub, go!
Thank you, sir.
[LANCE] You misunderstand.
This is for the city.
Dragon Lord Zaerog Armor!
[LANCE]
Cross-on!
Black Dragon's Wrath, activate!
[LANCE yells]
Time for you to go back.
You're finished!
Please, Ace... Wake up!
[CHARO sobs]
You have to!
Ace!
[TAMAZO]
Ace is in trouble, Tama!
So, does this mean he's
stepping out of the spotlight?
No way, Tama!
Next time! "The Path to
Guild Dragon Caller," Tama!
You've got a lot to learn
before you're stronger!