[NARRATOR]
For untold centuries,
there have been powerful
warriors who fought against
the various crises
that threatened our world.
They harnessed the power
of the monsters,
and forged a bond which
eased the planet's anger.
They were the Dragon Callers.
Dragon Callers are born
with the special power
to bridge the gap
between the realms
of nature, mankind,
and monsters.
When fear and hatred contaminate
the elements that surround us,
the Dragon Callers will
rise up with their monsters,
and restore balance
to our world.
Duen Desert. Home to a rare
monster with god-like powers.
Right.
If the monster accepts you,
things will be heavenly, tama,
but those forsaken turn
to sand and disappear.
Anyway, what's with that
outfit you're wearing?
I bought it at the gift
shop over there, tama!
Cool, huh? Took a picture in it!
We didn't come this
far to fool around!
[DAFNES] Trek across the sands
to the edge where the sun rises,
and you will find a monster
as powerful as a god.
Really?
Perhaps you might
succeed on this quest
where many others have failed.
[ACE]
I want to become stronger,
to be able to fight
alongside my monsters!
Let's go meet this
monster god, tama!
She said he's at the
Cavern of the Dragonoids.
Do you know where that is?
You bet I know the way!
Follow me, tama! Tama, tama!
Are you sure you're not
going to get us lost?
Yuck, it's so hot, tama!
I'm gonna turn into
a boiled egg, tama.
I know. How much longer
till we get to the cavern?
We'll be there real soon.
Now keep quiet
and follow my lead.
Ah! I found it, tama!
Wait for me!
Look at all this food, tama!
So delicious! I feel refreshed!
I thought you were leading
me to the god-monster!
Instead, you led me to food.
Don't be ridiculous.
In the desert, food and water
are gifts from the gods.
That really hit the spot, tama!
Hey!
Empty? Did you really just
finish off all our water?!
That was good,
and now I feel full.
You selfish little brat!
We still have a long way to go!
We were supposed to ration this!
Take it easy,
I just needed a pit stop.
Getting so livid about
such a trivial matter
is a bit of a
character flaw, tama!
You're making me angry, Tamazo.
That's too bad,
'cause you don't have a hope
of finding the place
without me, tama!
And if you've got a problem
with that, go find it yourself!
Yeah? Fine. I won't ask
for your help anymore!
It isn't my fault if
you end up lost, tama.
And there aren't
any dumpling shops
or ice cream vendors out there.
That's enough!
Tama.
I'm serious about this, Tamazo!
I'll find it on my own. I will.
You'll be sorry. Tama's
being serious about it, too!
I'm so thirsty.
Where is this place?
I've gotta find it.
[ACE] Whaddaya want?
I told you not to follow me.
I'm fine. I don't need Tamazo.
[TAMAZO] Hmph. There's no way he
can find the cavern by himself!
He should just give up and
come back to me, tama!
I'm getting bored!
Oh, I know!
Time for a little fun!
Chase the tail, tama!
Oh boy, I'm super
dizzy now, tama!
[screams]
[gasps]
Wait, you're not
doing anything either!
Wanna play with me, tama?
Are you tellin' me to bug off?
[gasps]
A bug saying "Bug off"?
[laughs]
Come on, that pun's gotta be
worth a little chuckle, Ace.
[TAMAZO]
Oh.
You're really lucky to have
a place to go home to, tama.
[TAMAZO]
Tama.
Ow!
He was chowing down on these
like they were delicious.
Tamazo is such a total weirdo.
Maybe I was too
harsh. I'm sorry.
[TAMAZO]
Ace. Ace!
Wake up, tama! Now's not the
time to be playing dead, tama!
Tamazo?
[TAMAZO]
Right over here, Ace!
Ace. Look! I'm over here, tama!
Hey, Tamazo!
Just face it, Ace, you can't
do anything without my help!
That's not entirely true.
I can do plenty on my own.
But what I said to you was
too harsh. Please forgive me.
[TAMAZO] Drink this,
and let's head back.
I got more water from
the oasis for you, tama!
Dude, thank you!
I was seriously thirsty.
Drink this and
let's head back home.
I need you to promise me, tama.
But why? We came
here to find him.
We won't leave until we've
found the god monster.
We don't even need him, tama!
Everything's fine the way it is!
We came out here because
I'm trying to become stronger!
Time to head home!
I'm not going any further!
Cut it out! Why are you
behaving like this?
Because you already have
us on your side, tama!
You get this god,
then more will join,
and they're all gonna be strong.
When that happens, you'll have
plenty of tough monsters!
And when you have enough,
you won't need me anymore!
Tama.
[ACE]
You've got it wrong.
Tama?
I do?
It isn't like that.
It's backwards.
I'm dragging you and the
other monsters down with me
because I'm not strong enough.
You, Ouka, and the others, you
always end up having to save me.
Hey, wait a sec. Is that why
you kept acting so obnoxiously?
That's right, tama!
I was trying to make
you cry, tama!
I was gonna keep doing it until
you gave up and went home!
Because... I didn't wanna
get thrown off the team.
Turned back into a Drop.
Tucked away somewhere
and forgotten about, tama!
Don't be dumb, Tamazo.
You called me dumb!
You think I'm stupid, tama?
No, it's just--
No! I heard you! I'll be
the first one off the team!
Calm down!
[SONIA]
It's you.
What are you doing
all the way out here?
Sonia?
[ACE]
That hit the spot!
You're a real life saver, Sonia!
Thanks for your help.
I came here to check on
the condition of the Drops.
It's lucky I found you.
Why are you here?
The Ancient of Dark, Master
Dafnes, told me of this place.
And that in this cavern
lived a god-like monster.
So I traveled here to find him.
Dafnes? I see.
I know this place, tama!
This god is
definitely here, tama.
You're in the Cavern
of the Dragonoids,
the god's sacred resting ground.
We've been protecting
it for generations.
This is it.
That one looks like Tamazo.
Well, they're both Tamadras.
Scores of them used to
live here in days gone by.
So there were a
bunch of Tamazos?
Sounds like a headache.
Sonia, what happened to Tamazo's
friends? Where'd they go?
I don't know.
One day they all
just disappeared.
Something's written
on it, tama!
[SONIA] "When the power of the
world's Drops becomes tainted,
the planet shall will its
messenger into action.
He will awaken all creation,
unlocking power beyond
comprehension."
It's an ancient legend
about the Tamadras.
I'm confused.
Tamadras are very
mysterious monsters.
They can speak with
Dragon Callers
and enhance their skills.
It is said that they carry
the planet's will with them.
Come to think of it, you fell
from the sky, didn't you?
I don't remember much, tama.
I guess you wouldn't.
Does that mean Tamadras
are the god-like monster
Master Dafnes told me about?
No, there is another monster.
Called Horus.
Horus?
[SONIA]
He guides Dragon Callers,
and blesses them with his power,
but gaining Horus' acceptance
is not an easy task.
And if he doesn't
accept you? What then?
The flame of his disapproval
will burn you to ashes.
You'll find Horus
down this hall.
Are you ready to face him, Ace?
You're gonna be
just fine, tama!
I'll be beside you
the whole time!
Right. Let's go.
A dead-end?
[TAMAZO]
Tama.
[ACE]
That must be Horus.
[HORUS]
Why have you come here?
[ACE gasps]
Because I'm trying
to become stronger.
I don't wanna just
rely on my allies.
I would rather fight
alongside them!
Please bless me with your power!
[HORUS] You already have the
powers of a Dragon Caller.
However, that still
won't be enough.
What is it that I'm lacking?
[ACE gasps]
Hey, is that Ancient Dragon
Knight's Soul Armor
you got there?
You can't hope to
take me on with that.
Is it my Soul Armor?
Sir, would a new Soul
Armor do the trick?
[HORUS] True power cannot
be viewed outwardly.
If you don't even
understand that much,
then you don't belong here!
No, please wait!
Mighty Horus,
tell me what I need!
Time to fight, tama!
Show him your true power,
and he's got to accept you!
Release!
Cross-On!
Water beats fire. Leviathan!
Blizzard Rise Charge!
He's strong!
[screams]
Ace! No!
Not so fast, tama!
Cross-On, tama!
Awesome!
Tamazo!
Soul Armor skill, go!
Wood Drop change!
We did it!
Oh, no.
[gasps]
[screams]
Tamazo!
You okay?
Please, no.
It wasn't supposed
to be like this.
Wake up, Tamazo!
Oh, Ace.
Tamazo is just fine, tama.
I can... I can
still fight, tama.
It's finished.
I can't keep fighting like this.
[TAMAZO] Ace, tama. You have
more strength than you realize.
Tamazo believes in
your power, Ace.
You can do it, tama.
Tamazo.
We all believe in you, tama.
You guys.
They're all saying,
"Don't give up," tama.
They want to work together.
I'll fight alongside you guys.
Now please, lend me your
power one more time!
I sense a significant
amount of energy.
Ace, grab that orb, tama!
I never knew Soul Armors
had such power.
All right! Let's go!
[ACE yells]
How the heck did I just do that?
[HORUS]
You've obtained the Cross Drop.
It's created when
the Dragon Caller
and the monsters' powers
work in perfect harmony.
But I was just desperate.
[HORUS]
You were so focused
on seeking out
strength for yourself,
you forgot one of the
most important things
a Dragon Caller can know.
What important thing is that?
[HORUS]
The strength of the bond.
Dragon Callers cannot become
more powerful on their own.
They must listen to the
voices of the monsters.
Only then can they hope
to unify their powers.
That is the true way.
And now, boy with the Tamadra,
I shall grant you my soul.
Protect this planet with
the strength of the bond!
[ACE]
I will.
[TAMAZO]
We did it, tama!
You got his Soul Stone!
Yeah.
It looks like you
found your answer.
Oh, hey Sonia.
Fire, wood, water,
light, and darkness.
When the individual
powers unite as one,
they'll complement one another,
and create an immense
amount of energy.
That's Horus' ability.
But weaving the different
energies together?
That's all up to you.
Right!
[gasps]
[TAMAZO]
Tama.
This is so comfy, tama!
I remember.
Oh, I've got it!
I can feel the power
flowing into my tail!
[gasps]
[TAMAZO]
Oh! Awesome!
Hino Kagutsuchi Tamazo!
Yo!
[ACE gasps]
Whoa! He changed?
Those are all
Tamadra egg shells.
The spirit of Hino Kagutsuchi
is embedded in the empty husks.
So Tamazo's got his own
Soul Armor now? Awesome!
[TAMAZO]
Yo!
[ACE chuckles]
Ow, that's hot!
Learn to use your new
power. Become stronger.
Impress me.
Armor Drop, tama!
I have Horus' power!
And you also still
have me too, tama!
Tamazo will make a great Dragon
Caller out of Ace yet, tama!
And I'm gonna stick by
your side until I do, tama!
Thanks, buddy.
First off, we need to
win the Battle Cup, tama.
You can do it if you put
your heart in it, tama.
Yeah. We'll do it
together, Tamazo.
[TAMAZO]
Tama!
[stomach growls]
Man, my stomach's super
growly all of a sudden.
I have a sunny-side up
egg ready to go!
What? How?
I cooked it using
Horus' flame, tama!
Fresh and tasty!
[TAMAZO chuckles]
[ACE]
You mean during--?
You need to take this
more seriously, you know!
[TAMAZO]
Oh, I am, tama.
That's why I only cooked
it over easy, tama.
[TAMAZO] The mighty Horus
has accepted Ace, tama!
I'm pretty sure it's all
thanks to me, tama.
Now that we've got
Horus' Soul Armor,
we're gonna win this
tournament, tama!
Next time. "Battle Cup Begins!"
Tama! Our opponent is
very surprising, tama!