[NARRATOR]
The Battle Cup,
where ambitious young Dragon
Callers come to compete against
one another and determine
who's the best of the best.
It's a high-stakes tournament
where matches are fought
based on fighter classes.
They're all competing
for the glory,
as well as the Golden Egg.
The late Ancient of Light,
Master Lukes, banned Soul Brave,
an ancient Dragon
Caller technique.
However, that ban was lifted
by the current Ancient
of Light, Master Jest.
Utilizing their Soul Armor
and various monsters,
these Dragon Callers are aiming
to bring home the big win!
Ready yourselves, challengers,
for the moment of truth!
[METAL]
There it is! The Cross Drop!
It can't be! [growls]
[yells]
Prism Feather Sword Attack!
[KLEIN groans]
[METAL] We're in the second
round with Class C,
and Ace's opponent, Logan,
hasn't bothered to
make an appearance!
If Logan doesn't show,
he will be disqualified,
and Ace will be the winner!
Well, this was unexpected.
I'd have brought
a book if I knew
we were gonna
have to wait, tama!
Maybe my irrepressible charisma
made him question his self-worth
and he decided to
run away, tama!
What's the matter, Ace?
I feel like I've
seen him before,
but I can't quite
remember from where.
You're gonna miss
Ace's match, devi.
Yeah.
Wait, aren't you
even interested?
Why would I care about
what happens to him?
[sighs]
[LOGAN]
Oops, sorry pal!
Watch where you're goin'!
Are you all right, Master Lance?
Uh...?
[gasps]
[LOGAN groans]
Hey, he's supposed to be
facin' Ace in the ring, devi!
[gasps] Now I recognize you.
Master Lance, you know
this guy, devi?
Yeah.
He's the guy we caught
trafficking Egg Drops.
It looks like you haven't
learned your lesson.
Somebody asked me to do it.
Then who are you working for?
I never met the guy!
I was offered a lot of money
for any Egg Drops I could grab.
And that's it! I swear!
Uh. Lance? What is this?
[LOGAN grunting]
Hang on!
Come on! Hurry it up!
[LIZARD chuckles]
Gah.
Who were those two?
A couple of Egg Drop
traffickers.
He'd entered the tournament,
was supposed to fight Ace,
but was out here stealing
Egg Drops instead.
How alarming. I'm glad
you recovered them.
I'll catch them.
Forget them.
What are you saying?!
We can't just let 'em
get away, devi!
Leave this unpleasant
matter in my hands,
you just focus on
the tournament.
I have very high hopes
for you, Lance.
All right.
[ANNOUNCER 29A]
In Class C, round two,
Logan's absence counts
as a withdrawal,
so Ace will win the
match by default.
[CROWD cheers]
I can't believe there was an
Egg Drop trafficking ring
operating right
under our noses!
I've heard rumors of
these traffickers,
this is troubling news indeed.
It's unfortunate that we
weren't able to catch them.
[VAHATON]
There seems to be a bad flow
swirling around this place.
First, the unbanning of
the Soul Brave technique,
and now these Egg Drop
traffickers appear.
This year's Battle Cup
is a real rollercoaster!
If Ace can win this next round,
he's gonna make it
to the finals!
Yes, but his next
battle is against...
Against Charo,
but he'll need to keep his
focus no matter who he faces.
Or else he'll learn the hard
way that you can't judge
a Dragon Caller's strength
by their appearance.
I'm sensing a lot
of tension in here.
I know! I'll bet I can
lift their spirits
with Tamazo's patented
tama-tama-dance, tama!
[groaning] Hey,
what's the big idea?!
Pipe down.
Leave these guys alone, for now.
[TAMAZO]
Tama!
[door slams]
I'm getting a little
nervous about our match.
Me, too.
My mom and dad are here,
and have a couple seats
up in the stadium.
I told them not to
bother coming out,
but they insisted on
watching anyway.
Of course they wanted to watch,
it's your first Battle Cup.
"I know I'm just going
to lose anyway.
I don't have a single hope
of winning this thing."
That's what I was thinking
when I first got to the arena.
But I don't think
that way anymore.
I want to win this.
After watching the way you
and Tiger fought each other,
I decided to try
like I actually had
a shot at winning my
first Battle Cup.
Charo...
It sounds pretty
ridiculous, doesn't it?
You're the only person I
could tell these thoughts to
who wouldn't just
laugh in my face.
But that isn't ridiculous!
We've already come this far
because of all the hard
work we've put in!
That's true.
I'm 100% in!
Let's give it
everything we've got!
Agreed. Let's fight to win!
Look, Father. It's Charo.
Best of luck, Charo!
Aren't you even worried
about our son?
Now, now, Mother.
Charo's already serving as an
official Guild Dragon Caller.
I know.
Take your seats, Class C's
next match is about to begin!
The two fighters squaring
off are Ace and Charo.
Friend against friend,
this could very well become
quite the heated confrontation!
[CROWD cheers]
Hey, Ace! Break a leg!
Charo! Show that city
boy what you've got!
Both sides ready.
Then it's Cross Fight time!
[ACE]
Cross-On!
Cross-On, tama! Ha!
Oh! Awesome!
[TAMAZO] Let's win this round
and head to the finals, Ace!
Yeah.
[CHARO]
Cross-On!
[GIRL 30A]
So cute!
[MAN 30A] He's using Fortoytops
to go head to head
with Horus' Soul Armor? Well, we
know who's gonna win this fight.
You never disappoint, Charo!
You're looking extra cuddly!
Try not to lose right away!
Otherwise, no one's
gonna believe
you're a real Guild
Dragon Caller!
[BOYS laugh]
I don't see you down here!
[CHARO]
Don't mind them.
But, Charo.
They don't understand.
Fortoytops entrusted
his soul to me.
That's why I'm giving this
battle everything I've got.
Do me a favor, and don't
hold back on me, Ace.
Fight me like you fought Tiger.
I wanna test myself against
your Soul Brave's power!
Fine by me.
My monster allies.
I'm going to need you to lend
me your power in this fight.
Ready?
Now, Release!
Horus Soul Brave, activate!
[HORUS squawks]
Ace demonstrates his
strength with Soul Brave!
[TORLIE]
Wood elements are at a natural
disadvantage against Fire.
Not to mention, that Ace
is using Soul Brave.
I wonder how Charo plans to turn
this bad situation around?
I won't let you use
Horus' ability!
[ENJU chirps]
Enju! Pipo Pipo Twister!
All right. Now it's my turn!
Not quite, you might
get interrupted!
Toyceratops, use
your Guard Stance!
Wood!
[TOYCERATOPS roars]
[TOYCERATOPS growls]
This time, for sure!
Okay! Get Ready!
I always am!
Enju, unleash Wind Spiral!
[gasps] The Drops. They changed!
[ACE groaning]
Charo throws consecutive
blows at his foe!
No one expected Ace to be
the first knocked down!
[CROWD cheers]
It's time to get up, come on!
[groaning]
That's it?
What an unexpected
turn of events!
Though he started the battle
with an elemental disadvantage,
Charo seems to have
the upper hand!
Oh, wow.
Charo's stronger than I thought!
He's definitely clever.
He's preventing
Horus' leader skill
by making a constant barrage
with his monster's skills.
What do you mean?
[ANGENE] With Horus, forming
combos of four or more elements
boosts your attack
power roughly twelvefold.
But Charo changes the
Drop colors so quickly,
Ace can never make an attack.
[BOTH]
Oh! I get it now!
What do you mean,
"you get it now"?
You're Dragon Callers!
You should've
already known that!
Nice work, Charo.
The timing on activating
your skills was perfect!
Thanks, Ace.
This is no time for
compliments!
You're not able to use
Horus' power, remember?!
Yeah, I know.
But this battle's
only getting started.
I'm fighting until the end!
[yells]
[MYSTIC STONE KNIGHT roars]
That's it! Cream him, Charo!
Rip him apart!
Whoa! Easy.
All right.
Power of the White Dragon!
[BABY WHITE DRAGON roars]
Let's go!
[MYSTIC STONE KNIGHT groans]
[ACE yells]
[yells]
No! Dryad!
[CHARO screams]
[groans]
Charo!
Ace strikes back, a solid hit!
[CROWD murmurs]
But Ace and Charo are friends.
That's why he hit him.
It was out of respect, they
aren't gonna pull any punches.
This battle,
it isn't over just yet!
I can keep fighting!
[TAMAZO]
Time to finish this, Ace.
Yeah. That's why we came here.
[yells]
[CHARO yelps]
[TAMAZO]
Keep going!
[ACE yells]
[gasps]
[ALL gasping]
[yelling]
[gasps]
It won't work!
[TAMAZO]
What's the matter?
Don't know!
For some reason, my monsters
aren't responding!
Ace is having difficulty
finishing the match
because he's afraid
he might hurt Charo.
Which is why he's unable
to synchronize with Horus.
He wouldn't be able to fully
control Soul Brave.
Hey, Ace!
Don't make the mistake of
underestimating my monsters!
Now, Dryad! Use Cure!
We promised, swore to
give it our best!
Charo.
There's no way I'm
just gonna give up!
Because watching you and Torlie
taught me an important lesson.
[CHARO]
That if you put your mind to it,
dreams really can come true!
[CHARO]
That even though I felt weak,
I could change myself!
That's why I fight to win!
Charo...
Mystic Knight!
Transform Drops... Wood!
And with that, Charo is
flooded with Wood Drops!
Will he end this in one strike?
Charo...
Come on! You can do it!
[TAMAZO] We can't let
him land this attack!
Ace, you have to become
one with Horus!
With Horus?
[TAMAZO]
Express how you feel!
Charo's serious,
you have to be too!
[gasps]
Tiger Combo Attack!
Tiger Jumping Shot!
Fire Horn Strike!
Tiger Kick!
[groans]
[chuckles] So what's
the deal, Ace?
Are you pulling your punches
just because we're friends?
[ACE] No way, I'm serious
about this too!
[TIGER]
I finally get it.
Right here!
I have to focus on
making my heart mighty,
to an infinite degree!
My monsters and my armor
will respond in kind
to the strength in my heart!
Right. My heart.
I made you a promise to
give it all I've got!
Get ready, Ace. Here goes!
[yells]
Celestial Eye... of Wadjet!
[gasps]
[CHARO screams]
Round three has ended.
The victor, Ace!
[CROWD cheers]
Charo!
I'm so proud of you, Charo!
Ace turned it around!
Yes, he did!
You were both awesome!
Well done, guys!
[ACE]
Charo!
Ace.
Don't worry. I'm fine.
[BOY 8A]
Yo! Charo! Hey!
[BOYS cheering, laughing]
You guys.
We're sorry for when
we called you a liar!
Come back to Libria
soon, Charo!
We'll be waitin' for ya!
Yeah, you've got it!
You showed the world
the strength of your
fighting spirit.
And that changed the way
those boys felt about you.
You both did very well,
and should be proud.
Thanks, Torlie.
I found the strength I
needed because of Charo.
It was the only way I could
became one with Horus.
Really?
Charo's spirit is what made
us find Soul Brave, tama!
You know, you're even
stronger than I expected.
Hold onto that strength
the rest of the way.
'Cause I know you
can win this, Ace.
[ACE] Yeah. Thanks for
believing in me.
I should thank you.
You fought me with
everything you had,
which means you
believed in me, too!
[CROWD cheering]
[footsteps]
Charo.
[CHARO]
I never expected this.
I had no idea losing
would be so frustrating.
Hey, man, that's proof you
tried your very hardest.
The best thing for you
right now is a good cry!
To scream at the
top of your lungs!
No, I just can't.
I'm not like you, Tiger.
[cries]
I'll cry with you!
'Kay buddy?
[cries]
[BOTH sob]
Now!
That brings us to the final
match-up for Class C!
The fighters are Ace, the
up-and-coming young rookie,
and his opponent: from the
Dark City, it's Kroell!
[VAHATON] So, it would appear
that Ace has mastered Soul Brave
just in time to advance
into the finals.
I'd expect no less
from King's son.
But his next opponent
is tricky to say the least.
This boy, Kroell,
he's quite dangerous.
[DAFNES] Consumed by
the forces of darkness.
[METAL] Class B has also
moved on to their finals!
Garnet versus Starjohn!
Which of them will take
the crown of victory?!
And the next match
in Class A will be...
...Morgan versus Herriot!
A battle between sisters!
[MORGAN] I've won 15 times
against my sister,
and lost 15 times, but today,
I'm ending the deadlock!
Using my Soul Brave, of course.
Next time:
"Dragon Caller of
Light and Dark."
Grab your popcorn,
I'll show you what a
Class A battle looks like!