I don't know why,
but I saw Drops that day.
[gasps]
I failed... I wasn't
strong enough...
Well. Callers who can draw
that many Drops at once
are few and far between.
Interesting.
[ACE] I wasn't good enough.
I can't let that happen again!
I need to get stronger.
I have to!
[HERRIOT]
You wanna be stronger?
[gasps]
[ACE]
Who're you?
When I toss this mapple,
gravitational forces
will pull it down.
But Dragon Callers
control Drops.
By matching Drops, we can
channel the various energies
that make up the natural world.
That's where the power that
Dragon Callers wield comes from.
And you are...?
This is my Dragon Caller
master, the Ms. Herriot!
If you really wanna be stronger,
the only way to do it
is through training.
Training? If you train me,
I'll be stronger?
Montage time!
Tama?
[whimpers]
So, uh...
Sorry, what?
Will you train me? I promise to
give it everything I've got!
Maybe I will.
But there's something
I need you to do for me
before we get started.
There's so many of them, Tama!
[HERRIOT] The locals call
this place Seashell Bay.
From what's washed ashore
I'm sure you can see why.
[ACE] And you only want me to
bring you the seashells
that have the moon mark on them?
No way we could
ever do that, Tama!
[gunshot booms]
--[ACE wails]
--[TAMAZO] Tama!
[MORGAN giggles]
[gasps]
Hey, careful with that!
Are you being naughty
and talking back to me?
I might have to punish you
if that's the case.
I told you to stop pointing
that dangerous D-Gear at people!
It's completely unprofessional!
Sister, dear, you're
always such a wet blanket!
I just like the sound,
so I loaded it with blanks.
No need to worry.
I want you to bring me as
many of these moon-shells
as you can find, and I'll
make an adorable necklace!
Won't you help me?
Ugh. Yes! Okay,
I'll do it! Sure thing!
But you're gonna train me
once I find them, aren't you?
I suppose.
Man. I haven't found any
seashells with moon marks.
Have you?
[HERRIOT]
What are you doing?
[TAMAZO]
Why did you do that, Tama?!
Ace spent a whole lot of time
sorting through those, y'know!
Waste of time.
Just look at it and see it.
Just look?
Yeah, right. There's no way
that's gonna work!
[GARNET]
Hmph.
Don't just give up and
say you can't do something
when you haven't even tried.
[gasps]
Come back tomorrow.
Huh?
Well, that's strange.
It turned all foggy.
[CHARO] Ace?
Are you feeling any better?
[ACE] Yeah, a little
ache-y here and there,
but I'm fine.
You helped me to safety after
I got knocked out, didn't you?
Thanks, Charo!
No need! Besides... I, uh...
I'm sorry.
Huh?
I just... I kinda feel guilty
for everything I said.
You thought you could win
and it's all my fault.
No way! It's my fault for
letting my power go to my head!
You haven't even filled your
D-Gear up with monsters yet.
There's no way you could've
taken down a monster
of that size with
an incomplete roster.
Charo...
[HERRIOT] Today, you're going to
weed the yard around my cottage.
[TAMAZO] She's just making
you do her chores for her!
--Bang!
--Tama! I'm sorry!
Don't talk back, cue ball.
Phoo.
[HERRIOT] And my little sister
also has a task
for you to complete.
[MORGAN] Since you're going to
be weeding her yard anyway,
could you keep an eye out
for a four-leaf clover?
Lucky clovers are going
to be all the rage
in women's fashion this season!
[ACE] And you'll train me
if I find it for you?
[HERRIOT]
Maybe we will.
[growls]
[ACE]
None here... None here.
Man! These are all
three leaves.
[HERRIOT] What? Are you ready
to throw in the towel?
[ACE grunts]
No!
But aren't ones with
four leaves really rare?
So...
If you listen to the voice of
nature, I know you can find it.
Oh, yeah?
Is the grass gonna say
"There's a four-leaf clover
over here, Ace"?
What a buncha hogwash.
[yelps]
Tama!
Don't get sassy with me,
husky britches!
[HERRIOT giggles]
Who's the softest,
squishiest little cutie-pie
in the whole wide world, huh?
[gasps]
I could see them again
for a second...
[groans]
[giggles]
[ACE] Oh, man, I'm calling it
for today. I'm exhausted!
[TAMAZO] What point
is there in weeding
that weirdo's yard, Tama?
Look, I'm afraid she's
just using you, buddy.
[GARNET]
You want training, don't you?
[TAMAZO]
Tama?
Don't you want to be a certified
Guild Dragon Caller?
[slurps]
Of course you want that.
I dunno, maybe.
How's Guild Dragon Calling
different from what I'm doing?
Man, you don't know
anything, do you?
One's Guild-affiliated
and the other's solo.
When you join the Guild,
they try to assign you tasks
suited to your
specific skill set.
Then... Lance came to
Vienna City on Guild business?
Resolving a Drop Impact
is one of the most
important tasks assigned
to a Guild Dragon Caller.
Could you help me out
with something?
One of my monster's
Egg Drops is all cloudy.
You see?
Yes, that certainly
is a problem.
This Mystic Dark Knight
wants to become stronger.
But I'm afraid you aren't
strong enough for him to grow.
But I can change that...
If I just train to be stronger,
the Mystic Dark Knight
will get stronger, too?
It's all up to you.
[ACE]
My poor belly's rumbling.
[gasps]
[ACE]
I can't really explain why.
Some of 'em just sparkle.
[ACE]
I see it! It's the same sparkle!
[TAMAZO gasps]
Tama!
Found one!
With the moon mark!
[beeping]
What's this?
Huh? I got a message.
Oh, yeah, that's right, the
Guild Dragon Caller's exam
is this week.
So are you planning to try out?
[DRAGON CALLER A]
No way!
The Guild Dragon
Caller's exam?
[ACE] "Attention prospective
Guild Dragon Callers:
there's an exam at
the glacier tomorrow."
I wish I was ready
to go and take the exam.
[HERRIOT]
You're not gonna try?
Uh. Well, no. I still
have to go through training.
You just finished
your training, Ace.
[ACE]
Huh?
Wow, nicely done!
[TAMAZO]
I knew it, Tama!
They were just taking
advantage of you!
You worked the whole day
without complaint.
Driven on by your focus
on your given mission.
You followed your instincts
and you never gave up.
Important traits for
pro Dragon Callers.
You'll be able to control
the flow of Drops
with more training, and then
you can bend it to your will.
Never forget this lesson.
Uh? Sure...
And now here's a little reward
for all the hard work
you've done.
[ACE]
That's an Egg Drop! Awesome!
Now I've got another
monster in my D-Gear,
which means my team's
even stronger!
Don't let it go to
your head, Tama...
Whoah--Oh!
You're such a trouble-maker!
I could say the same
thing about you, Tama!
What's up with the jacket?
Well, tomorrow's
exam site is some place
that's supposed
to be pretty cold.
[knocking]
Charo.
Hey, so, I guess you're
planning to take the exam?
You, uh, wouldn't mind if I
tagged along for it, would you?
You, too?
I can't see the Drops
clearly most of the time,
and I don't have my own D-Gear,
so I can't take the exam.
But I still want to
come along and help you out
in any way I can!
Of course you can come!
With you on my team,
I know I'll pass the test!
[CHARO]
Heh. Yeah!
It's--It's freezing!
[sniffs]
My nose is stopped up!
[CHARO]
It's Mister Metal!
Hello, all! I'll be
proctor in charge
of directing today's
Guild Dragon Caller
Glacier Examination Event!
My name is Metal.
It's a pleasure to meet you!
Look! That's the Ancient
of Water over there!
Oh, heya, Vahaton!
If you're here
to take the exam,
please head to the indicated ice
cave, where we can get started.
Uh! Excuse me!
I'm not taking the exam!
[gasps]
Oh, no!
[ACE]
[CHARO]
They barricaded the entrance...
Aw, these little
tykes are too cute!
So, you kids wanna grow up
to be Dragon Callers?
Yeah, we're just kids.
But that doesn't give you the
right to be condescending!
Are you planning to take
the exam, too, old timer?
Yes, and I'm hoping this year,
I'll have what it takes
to pass the exam.
Heya, pops. Wanna clue us in on
what the exam's gonna be like?
Come on, you can share.
Well, the exam's actually
been completely different
every single time I've taken it.
It's nothing to brag about,
but I've taken this test
many times over the
course of 20 years,
and they have yet
to recycle anything.
Heh. Then you're useless.
You mean you've taken
this exam hundreds of times?
No. It used to only take place
every four to five years or so,
as I recall. But now they hold
the exam more frequently
than they did in the old days.
Which is good news
for me, really.
All right, it's time to
get this exam underway!
If you'd all please pick one of
the rooms in front of you
and step right in.
I had no idea
so much showmanship
was involved in the exam.
[DONNY]
Hmph. So what is this?
[METAL] Now, there should be ice
walls in front of everyone.
You'll need to get to the
other side if you want to
move on from this room.
[VAHATON] Be sure to
choose a course of action
based on the very nature of
what you see before you.
For those of you
who choose correctly,
you'll reach the other side
of the Ice Cave Wall
and the next part of the test.
[WALTER grunting] All you have
to do is get to the other side?
Then I'll break it down!
[grunts]
[METAL] Please, proceed
carefully however,
as you will be
penalized any time
the action you
take is incorrect.
I wish you'd said that sooner...
[DONNY sighs]
[groans]
No. It won't budge!
[DONNY] Did the rock
next to it slide over?
I get it! It must work
the same as Drops!
So all I've gotta do is line up
the same colors up like always!
[groans] That's weird.
I-It won't slide!
[DONNY groans]
[screams]
It must behave like
a Drop. Here goes!
[HENDERSON grunts]
[HENDERSON groans]
I failed again!
[TAMAZO] It won't line up
like the usual Drops do.
And adding a third Drop doesn't
make it disappear either, Tama.
[CHARO]
What should we do now, Ace?
[VAHATON] Be sure to
choose a course of action
based on the very nature
of what you see before you.
For those of you
who choose correctly,
you'll reach the other side
of the Ice Cave Wall
and the next part of the test.
The nature... of what you see.
I want to make that plant grow.
But I'm not getting
any Wood Drops in here.
I've got it!
The Ancient Dragon Knight has a
skill that transforms
Fire Drops into Wood Drops,
and that just might be
your way outta here!
'Kay. It's time for
me to Cross-On! [yells]
Drop Change skill! Wood!
You did it, Ace!
Well done, Tama!
I thought I should listen
to nature's voice,
like in training!
Looks like I was right!
You did a great job, Ace!
[laughs]
[MYERS groans]
What are we supposed to do?!
There's no way
we can get across this!
[FRANK growls] I'll swim across
easily using my ninja magic!
[yells]
[grunting]
[screams]
I was wrong!
[METAL] That option
never would have worked!
[ACE] Ice all around...
Wait, that's it!
[ACE] I can use the Water Drops,
make all of it.
Go!
Come on! We don't
have much time!
--Right!
--Tama.
Well, then. That's one way
to get things done!
[VAHATON] There's always
more than one solution.
But the method they chose
is a little less
conventional than most.
[CHARO grunts]
We made it, Tama!
You just flew the whole time!
[ALL laugh]
Now! Everyone here
has passed the trials so far,
but, it's time for us to move on
to the next section of the exam!
[VAHATON] Your task is to make
your way through this room
without using any
of your monsters.
[BLUE TROLLS growl]
[MYERS]
So what?
Are they just gonna
stand there and not attack?
[BLUE TROLL A growls]
[MYERS growls, yells]
Hah! Guess I was
too strong for him!
Now for the rest of 'em!
No need! You've done enough
for us to make our decision!
Please step into the
adjoining room, sir.
Yeah? Seriously?
Well, then, adios, amigos!
Nice! It looks easier than
any of us were expecting!
Hey, what's the big idea?
Just take down one,
that way there's enough left
over for the rest of us!
[laughs] Sometimes the
wisest choice in competition
is to thin the herd.
If you boys hope to catch up,
then you'd better hurry,
or else there won't be
any Blue Trolls left!
I'm up next, right?
No way! I'm gonna go next!
Why won't the Blue Trolls
attack to push these guys back?
They just keep standing,
huddled around the same spot.
They're probably making a
barrier to protect the weaker,
smaller Blue Troll
in the back row.
[gasps]
Please stop!
Huh? What's wrong?
That coat cook your brain?
They're just trying to protect
the weakest ones in their group.
They aren't even fighting back!
It isn't fair! Leave them alone!
[MEADOWS] Hah!
Who cares about these wimps?
You came here to pass the exam
like everybody else, didn't ya?
Now move!
[ACE grunts] I told you
to leave them alone!
[grunts]
Get offa me, ya little freak!
Let go of me.
I said hands off!
[ACE grunts]
--Careful!
--Tama!
Yeah, don't mess with me, kid!
Charo, Tamazo!
Tama!
[CHARO grunts]
[BLUE TROLL B growls]
No, don't!
[ACE grunts]
[gasps softly]
The Troll...
Huh?! What the
heck was that?
I would've blasted that monster
for sure if this weirdo
hadn't run out in
front of my attack!
[VAHATON] Mm-hmm. If the
Blue Troll hadn't turned
into a Drop just now,
you would've defeated him,
there's no question about it.
Then...
Then please make your way
into the adjoining room.
That's that!
Smell ya later, kid!
I guess we were supposed
to defeat those Blue Trolls,
and we've failed the exam
because we didn't.
[ACE chuckles]
[ALL gasp]
[MYERS] It's about time!
So, what's the next test?
Well, that's it.
Your exam is over!
Uh? So does that mean what
I think it means, sir?
[VAHATON]
Yes, it does indeed.
I'm afraid the lot of you
ignored the voice of nature.
And that means you also
fail as Dragon Callers.
[gasping]
[ACE gasps]
This test is done,
and you have passed!
[ACE]
Huh?!
You passed the test, Ace!
I knew you could!
Looks like all your
training really paid off!
Hi, Ms. Herriot!
[HERRIOT]
Searching for the right seashell
and listening to what the
voice of the plants had to say.
Wasn't such a waste
of time, was it?
[ACE] Oh, so you used that
yard work to train me?
[HERRIOT] Yep. Well, that
and my yard was a mess.
Huh...?
I told you she was using you
to do her chores, Tama.
[VAHATON] Now that you've
proven that your heart's
in the right place, you may
proceed to the final test.
Wah! I wonder
what's gonna hatch?!
[CHARO] Whoa!
Your Mystic Dark Knight evolved!
Wow, I guess I really did
get a little bit stronger!
[MORGAN laughs]
[MORGAN] Jeez.
You are so naïve.
And the Guild
is no better, really.
That wasn't a real test at all.
[ACE growls]
[MORGAN]
Well, then.
I guess I'll have to be the one
to put you through the wringer,
you silly little boy.
[growls]
[ACE] I finally made it
to the last test!
And sure, I'm facing off against
a strong-looking Dragon Caller,
but I've got Tamazo, Ouka
and the rest on my side!
Next time!
"King's Footsteps."
I'm going to become
a Guild Dragon Caller!