[MAN A]
Hey, kid.
You got any money to help out
a guy down on his luck?
I don't need very much.
Just enough for a drink.
And I swear, I'll pay
you back soon enough.
[LANCE whimpers]
[MAN A]
Hey, kid! Wait!
You better run away!
Stinkin' brat!
[LANCE gulps]
Delicious!
Huh?
[DIANA]
Lance!
[PEOPLE screaming]
[DIANA]
Lance, where are you?!
[LANCE'S DAD]
Diana!
Lance is okay!
Get outta there!
--[LANCE whimpers]
--[LANCE'S DAD] Listen, Lance.
You stay here,
and don't move, understand?
[LANCE gasps]
[DIANA]
Lance!
[LANCE'S DAD]
I'm coming!
[LANCE whimpers]
[LANCE gasps]
[VOICE]
Devi...
[LANCE]
Huh...?
It's an egg. With a star?
I've gotta try to keep it warm.
[gasps]
[LANCE screams]
[LANCE whimpers]
[LANCE gasps]
[DEVI]
Devi...
Dev, dev, dev, dev...
[LANCE gasps]
[DEVI]
Devi.
Devi?
It's just water.
[sighs]
Devi?
Are you hungry?
Here, have some.
It's okay.
That was delicious!
[LANCE gasps]
You...
Did you just talk?
[DEVI]
What was that, devi?
It's called a pearapple.
Pearapple?
You just spoke.
I hope that's not a problem.
Not at all, but you just
hatched a few minutes ago.
It's amazing!
I am amazing.
Some more water?
No, thank you, devi.
So then, who are you, devi?
[LANCE]
My name is Lance.
Aren't you going to eat
something, too, Lance?
No.
I'll be all right.
[DEVI] Ah. That was the
only one you had, devi.
[LANCE]
It's okay.
I'll get another tomorrow.
You leaving?
Hey, Lance.
What's this thing?
I think that's just a rock.
[DEVI]
Can I eat it, devi?
No, it isn't edible.
[DEVI]
Devi.
And what's this?
[LANCE]
It's an empty can.
[DEVI]
Can I eat it, devi?
That one isn't edible either.
[DEVI]
Devi.
--[DEVI] How about this?
--[CAT yowls]
No, definitely
don't eat the cat!
[DEVI]
And this?
[LANCE]
I wouldn't even pick that up...
[DEVI]
I see...
What about this?
Can I eat this thing, devi?
[LANCE sighs]
I wouldn't.
[LANCE groans]
[grunts]
Oh, well, whatever.
It doesn't bother me.
Devi?
[gasps]
Just what I was looking for!
I'll grab one for Lance, devi!
Hey, now, you can't just
take my pearapples, buddy!
Hey! Let go, devi!
No way! This one can talk!
Hey, honey, guess what?
Our stall has attracted
a talking monster!
[OWNER WIFE] Yeah? So what?
That's nothing special.
Tweets down at the bird shop is
always running her mouth, too.
--Listen moustache-face!
--That's not the same thing!
--I said let me go, devi!
Tweets can only say
"good morning" and
"Tweets want a cracker."
And you... You tried to
steal my merchandise!
[DEVI]
Your merchandise?
Don't you play dumb with me!
You tried to run off
with one of my pearapples!
I needed it!
I ate the only one Lance had,
so I wanted to return the favor!
So, what kinda monster are you?
And do you have any money?
[DEVI]
Money?
Don't give me that!
I make my living
off selling fruit!
And if you want some,
you've got to give me cash!
Why are you talking about
the basic principles of
business at this hour?
[OWNER HUSBAND] I'm trying to
teach him some common sense!
[OWNER WIFE]
You, teaching common sense?
--Don't make me laugh!
--Money, huh?
[OWNER HUSBAND] You wanna
find a wild pearapple tree?
Gee, I dunno.
[OWNER WIFE]
Around this time of the season,
the only blooming tree you'll
find would be at Mount Kyomei.
[OWNER HUSBAND]
But Mount Kyomei's
two whole mountains
away from here!
We're talking
two day's travel, easy!
[DEVI]
I'm going.
Devi-vi!
I could still go on,
if my wings would just keep up!
Devi?
Devi! Devi, devi, devi, devi,
devi, devi, devi, devi, devi!
[gasps]
[LANCE sighs]
It doesn't matter...
[LANCE]
Hmm?
[DEVI]
Lance!
Lance, Lance, Lance!
Hey, Lance!
Are you still sleeping, devi?
Wake up, devi.
It's starting to get dark, devi.
Oh, hey, it's you again!
Are you sticking around?
Are you still hungry, devi?
How about a pearapple, devi?
But how?
Where'd you find 'em?
And so many!
[DEVI] You use money to buy
goods like pearapples, devi.
--How did you get money?
--[DEVI] I danced, devi.
I grooved my heart out to the
sweet, melodic jams, devi!
And my dancing brought in
a big audience, devi!
Everyone was laughing, devi!
Laughing and smiling,
full of joy!
They paid a lot of money
for the performance,
and Leader gave me
some of it, devi!
He's called Leader?
[DEVI]
That's what he said, devi.
[gasps]
You did a great job today, Devi!
Devi?
That should be your name!
Because you're always
saying "devi-devi."
[DEVI]
Devi?
[LANCE]
Hmm. Like it?
[DEVI]
It's a perfect name, devi!
Devi will be Devi from
this point onward, devi!
Devi, devi!
Devi-devi, devi-devi!
[sighs]
I need to call it a night, devi.
Leader says we're going to
perform in the next town over
tomorrow morning, devi!
[LANCE]
You're awesome, Devi!
[DEVI]
Devi is pretty amazing, devi.
[LANCE]
Are you tired?
[DEVI]
Nah, not at all!
I can do this kind of thing
all day long, devi!
I think Leader and the others
take too many breaks, devi.
That's just because
you're full of energy!
Is that a problem?
[laughs]
Thank you for everything.
I appreciate what you've done.
Appreciate, devi?
So, Lance appreciates Devi?
Sure, I do.
[DEVI] Then, maybe Devi is
Master Devi, now, devi.
What's that?
[LEADER A] Remember,
our customers are patrons
of the arts.
We should be respectful
to them and appreciate
what they provide.
Treat 'em like you
would a master.
[DRUMMER A] So you
gotta stop telling them to
"enjoy the show or else."
You're killin' the creative
spirit, little dude!
[DEVI]
Devi?
[BAND MEMBERS laugh]
Okay, then.
Master Devi!
Devi!
I'm starting to feel pretty
important now, devi.
Master Devi.
Thanks for your help!
Oh, I forgot!
I borrowed these
from Leader, devi!
Why?
A haircut!
I want to see Lance's
face better, devi.
Uh! No, thanks!
[DEVI] Leader and the other
fellas do it all the time, devi!
They even taught me how!
[LANCE]
But I don't want a haircut!
[DEVI]
Stop moving, devi!
[LANCE]
No! Don't!
[gasps]
[BOTH whimper]
[LANCE]
Sorry, did I frighten you guys?
It's okay. I'm not scary.
[gasp, laugh]
[LANCE chuckles]
[DEVI]
Lance!
[gasps]
Welcome back.
We can really treat
ourselves today, devi!
What would you like to eat?
Huh? Pearapple's fine.
Yeah, but these
are for dessert, devi.
What if you and I have
T-bone steak instead?
Whatever Master
Devi decides to have, I'll eat.
Devi? Then I'll
head to the store!
Dev-vi!
[DEVI]
Uh-oh!
One of our pearapples
has escaped!
Oh! Whoops!
[LANCE]
Devi! Not there!
Oh, no!
I guess Devi will have
to eat this one now, devi!
[DEVI]
Devi?
You know what?
You can keep it, devi.
[LANCE]
Devi!
[gasps]
What was that?
[LANCE]
Devi?
Devi! Devi!
Is something
the matter, Master Dafnes?
[DAFNES]
Summon the carrier dragon.
[DEVI]
Devi...?
Devi? Who are you?
[DAFNES sighs]
It looks like you survived.
Hey! Let go of my friend!
Watch your tongue!
This is the Ancient of Darkness,
Master Dafnes!
I never expected
to find a Devidra.
I find it rather hard to
believe you're serving the boy.
Were you cast away?
[DAFNES]
Look around.
He did this to protect you.
[DAFNES] I thought it was
another Drop Impact.
We simply can't
allow someone with this kind
of raw power to run loose.
He won't make it
without our help.
[DEVI whimpers]
[DAFNES] We're taking him
to the Water City.
You can't, devi!
Lance belongs here
with his Devi, devi!
Enough!
This all happened
because of you.
[LANCE pants]
[DAFNES]
Am I wrong?
But he's...
[DAFNES]
We must hurry.
Yes, ma'am!
Please wait!
He needs his hat and PJs!
They're still
in the wooden box
where he puts all his treasures!
The hat was his dad's!
And his mom sewed
those PJs for him, devi!
Also, something else-- Lance...
He's likely to catch a cold
if he sleeps with his tummy
not covered up, devi!
One of his back
right teeth is starting
to come loose, devi!
And sometimes, he scrunches
his face up and pretends
to be annoyed even though
he's really having a good time!
He also prefers to
have his eggs scrambled
instead of served
sunny-side up, devi!
But most importantly...
He's my friend.
[DEVI]
Lance!
[DEVI] Please, sir, can you just
tell me how he's doing, devi?
[DRAGON CALLER A] Master Dafnes
said that she doesn't
have time to see you.
[MAN A] Boss! I rounded
everyone up, like you wanted.
[DEVI] We've got all the
delinquents in town here.
Listen up. I just need you
to create a commotion
outside the mansion, devi.
[DEVI] But if you fools do
anything more than that,
you'll have earned yourself
a quick Devi-Devi-Punch
to the gut, devi.
[MAN B]
We definitely don't want that.
[DEVI] Time to get one
over on old lady Dafnes!
[MAN B] Uh, boss? There's a
Guild Dragon Caller out there,
and he's headed right for us!
[MAN A]
What the--?
[MAN C]
Was our plan leaked?
[MAN B]
What do we do?
[DEVI] We're not gonna let
some stinkin' Dragon Caller
scare us away!
[MAN A]
He's all alone!
[MAN B]
Then if we both attack him-
[LANCE]
Release!
You overdid it.
[MEN scream]
I'm afraid that all
your scheming ends here.
Dafnes wants to see you.
Come along quietly.
But I can't...
I just... devi.
Just hurry it up.
[DEVI whimpers]
Devi!
He's all grown up, and
he's a Guild Dragon Caller...
Even without Devi
around, he's fine.
Lance doesn't need Devi anymore.
[DEVI]
Devi...
How long are you
gonna make me wait?
[DEVI whimpers, cries]
[LANCE] Master Dafnes
made a special request
to the Guild about you.
[LANCE] You're to work
for us now, as my assistant.
[DEVI wails]
Devi! I'm so happy...!
And from now on...
...you're my Master.
And I'm never leaving
your side again, I swear! [sobs]
[ACE]
Wait, when did he get shot down?
[CHARO]
Just now.
He asked her out?
[CHARO]
That's right.
On the first day
we arrived in town.
Poor guy.
I didn't know any of that.
That's just classic Tiger, tama.
[ACE]
Hey, Lance. You here to eat?
Or you could just ignore me.
He's as annoying as usual, tama!
[CHARO]
Looks like Devi's not with him.
[ACE] He went to check in
on Master Vahaton.
[CHARO]
That was nice of him!
[TAMAZO]
He hurt his hip, tama!
'Cause he's older
than dirt, tama!
[ACE]
Stop that!
[DAFNES]
Do you fully understand?
Your role is crucial.
[DEVI]
Devi!
[DAFNES] You should
return to him quickly.
The last thing we want
is for Lance to catch on.
[DEVI]
Understood, devi.
[TORLIE]
What are Drops?
And how do they
give energy to monsters?
[TORLIE]
The world faces a crisis,
and I want to
explain things to you,
the Guild's newest
Dragon Callers.
Next time,
"The Secret of Drops."
Which is the secret
of our very world.