[NARRATOR]
The Battle Cup,
where ambitious young Dragon
Callers come to compete against
one another and determine
who's the best of the best.
It's a high-stakes tournament
where matches are fought
based on fighter classes.
They're all competing
for the glory,
as well as the Golden Egg.
The late Ancient of Light,
Master Lukes, banned Soul Brave,
an ancient Dragon
Caller technique.
However, that ban was lifted
by the current Ancient
of Light, Master Jest.
Utilizing their Soul Armor
and various monsters,
these Dragon Callers are aiming
to bring home the big win!
Ready yourselves, challengers,
for the moment of truth!
[CROWD cheers]
I'm bringing this match
to an end, right now!
Dark Hell Scythe!
Now Ace, attack
him from above!
You got it!
[KROELL growls]
God Burning Attack!
[grunts]
[KROELL yells]
[KROELL screams]
Which makes Ace the ultimate
victor in this match-up.
Which also makes him this year's
Battle Cup Class C Champion!
[CROWD cheers]
And now, we come to the finale
of the Battle Cup finals round!
The champion of
Class B is Starjohn,
and Ace defeated Kroell to
become the Class C champ.
But this next match is a doozy,
because we've at long last made
it to the finals of Class A!
The first contender
in this match
defeated her sister Morgan in a
hard-fought semi-finals bout
to make it here, it's Herriot.
Though she may have benefitted
from the unbanning
of the Soul Brave technique,
it was her courageous fighting
style that really helped
her go the distance!
Facing off against Herriot
in the finals for Class A,
it's last year's Battle Cup
champion, Lance!
And just like last year,
he has yet to break a sweat
on his path to the top!
Unlike many of
the top contenders,
he hasn't used Soul Brave in
any of his battles so far,
is this the quiet dignity
of a champion?
Will Lance secure his second
consecutive Battle Cup victory
at this year's tournament?
Or will Herriot finally realize
her long-held dream
of being crowned champion?
Every single one of us
is just dying to know.
This round can't
begin soon enough!
[CROWD cheers]
The Class A finals, a match
between the regulars.
"The regulars"?
Ah.
And whichever of them wins this
match, will face a rising star.
Either Class B's Starjohn,
or Ace from Class C.
That'll be an interesting
battle no matter who fights.
It's always encouraging to see
such promising young
talent rising up.
I wonder whether Lance will be
victorious this year as well.
[VAHATON]
Ah, yes.
I was wondering the same.
[LANCE]
It won't be much longer now.
Um, Master Lance?
Do you have a secret plan
for how to use Devi
in this fight, devi?
Business as usual, of course.
Defeat our opponent.
Devi would be proud to
follow Master Lance's
every command, devi!
I'll show Ace and
the White Dumpling
that our bond is stronger
than theirs, devi!
[LANCE]
Ace...
[ACE, TAMAZO]
Now, Yomi Wave!
[yells]
[KROELL screaming]
We've been allies on
the field of battle
for quite some time now.
Since the moment we first met.
Devi, too?!
Are you counting Devi, too?
[LANCE]
Hmph. Of course. I need you.
[DEVI] Ha, ha! Devi
will do my very best
to fight alongside
Master Lance, devi!
[KLEIN]
So, where you headed, darling?
[MORGAN]
Well,
I'm going to the arena to watch
my sister win, of course.
"Watch her win"?
So you think she can beat Lance?
Oh, without a doubt!
We battled in the semi-finals
to decide which of us
would get to beat Lance, and put
him in his place this year.
[KLEIN laughs]
Is that a fact?
I wonder if things will actually
go as easily as you expect?
[MORGAN]
Hmph.
I'm certain that Herriot will
put up a fierce resistance.
However, Lance is a
strong opponent.
What do you say we find a nice,
quiet place where the two of us
can be alone to talk
about this further--?
Ah...
[METAL] The Class A finals
will soon begin!
Lance and Herriot are both
in the ring, psyching up!
[CROWD cheers]
Something tells me
Lance probably has
his fight in the bag.
You watch your mouth!
My Master'll wipe
the floor with him!
No offense, but we're
talking about Lance, here!
But still, you can't
really be that sure.
[GARNET, TIGER]
Hm?
Ms. Herriot has already used
Soul Brave in the tournament,
which may give her an advantage
over Lance, who hasn't yet--
You hear that, lunkhead?
And Servant Number Two has
data to back his opinion up!
My professional insight
puts Lance to win
at seven to three odds, tama.
But I'm betting on
the dark horse, tama.
[ACE] So, both of them have a
decent chance to win this match.
[gasps]
[HERRIOT]
Watch me, Morgan.
I'm going to win this,
for both of us!
Good luck out there.
Now, without further ado,
let's get this match started!
Cross Fight!
Go!
[CROWD cheers]
Ha! Early bird catches the worm!
I'm going to try to get
this over with quickly!
Soul Brave!
Archangel Metatron!
[METAL] Herriot activates Soul
Brave right out of the gate!
[LANCE exhales]
[LANCE]
Soul Brave Zaerog!
What?!
[ZAEROG roars]
[METAL]
There we have it!
Lance just activated Soul Brave
for the first time
in the tournament!
Oh, yeah!
Lance is using Soul Brave, too?
[TAMAZO]
Tama!
He's serious.
[laughs] He must've realized
he needs to put some effort in
if he wants to win this match.
This is exciting!
Defeating you now should
be even more rewarding!
Here we go!
[HERRIOT yelling]
[METAL] Herriot continues
throwing punches!
Lance has no choice
but to play defense!
I won't stop! Ahh!
What's up?
Herriot's totally got Lance
up against the ropes!
Well, theoretically, Lance may
not be comfortable fighting
with Soul Brave yet. This is
his first attempt to use it.
No, not that.
[ALL]
Huh?
Wait. What's "not that," tama?
He's studying his opponent,
trying to get some insight
on her strategy.
[HERRIOT grunting]
Stop messing around with me!
I hate that smug face!
How can you be so
calm during this?!
[METAL] Oh! Lance is going
on the offensive now!
They're both furiously
attacking each other!
[HERRIOT] I knew you'd
keep me on my toes.
It's time for us to settle who's
stronger once and for all!
Holy Crest!
[METAL] Whoa! Herriot
activated Arcline's skill!
With Holy Crest, her attack
power has effectively doubled!
[HERRIOT yells]
[DEVI] Master Lance!
This isn't looking good, devi!
I'm not done!
[HERRIOT]
I won't lose.
I owe my sister that, at least!
[MORGAN, HERRIOT grunt]
Ha, ha! You've gotten quite
a bit stronger, Morgan.
That's because I've
been training hard
to win the next Battle Cup.
If anyone's gonna stop
your winning streak,
I want it to be me.
[laughs] Bring it on, Sis.
I'm gonna pulverize you!
Just you watch.
[CROWD cheering]
[METAL] The winner of
this year's Battle Cup
is the first-timer named Lance!
Having easily defeated the
twins, Herriot and Morgan,
he used his overwhelming
force to secure victory!
[MORGAN]
Come on, stop!
Get back here, Silver Fox!
I wanna rematch!
Herriot, you've got
to settle down!
[HERRIOT grunts]
[panting]
Enough, why don't
you call it a day?
Not yet.
I have to keep going until
I'm strong enough to beat him!
It's pointless to
keep trying to--
[HERRIOT grunts]
[HERRIOT]
Nothing is pointless!
You and I, we both worked
hard to come this far!
And that's why we can
take anybody down.
Isn't that right, Morgan?
Oh, Herriot.
You're always so serious
about everything, jeeze.
So next time around,
one of us is going to win.
Agreed?
Oh, yeah! It's a promise!
Both Morgan and I trained
hard for our chance
to beat you here today!
This time, the ban on
Soul Brave is over!
Which means I've got a
better chance of winning!
And now... Regulus,
use your skill!
Full Plasma Wave!
[METAL]
With that move,
Herriot changes all the Drops
to Water, Light, and Heart!
Way to go, Master!
She could pull off a big
attack with all of those!
Looks like Lance is
in a pickle, tama!
Devi, your turn.
Yeah, roger that!
Ah! Cross-On, devi!
Yeah! Devivebub, go!
[METAL] Is Lance finally
trying to return fire?
Devivebub is going for it!
Ha! Your cute little Devidra.
I'm going to squeeze on the
little guy more than usual!
Light Armajin!
[DEVI]
Devi?!
Devi failed you.
Devi's so sorry!
No need for that.
You did very well.
Devi?! Devi-vi!
When one attacks, the other
immediately throws
up their guard!
It's an advanced battle
between Class A Callers!
However, it's looking like
Herriot may have the upper hand!
[JEST]
Hm.
That's strange.
Lance appears cautious.
So it might seem.
No, look at his eyes.
They haven't changed a bit.
Careful, Lance.
All right, then!
Time to finish this!
Princess Valkyrie!
Attack Stance, Light!
[METAL]
But of course!
This is what she
was really after!
Having used Princess
Valkyrie's special skill,
Attack Stance Light, all the
Heart Drops around Herriot
have been transformed
into Light Drops!
That was clever.
For sure.
I agree! But why, though?
Instead of just creating
Light Drops from the start,
she made a bunch of
Heart Drops appear
so that she could transform
them into Light Drops
later when she needed them.
That way, she could put together
enough Light Drop combos
to make a major attack
right at the end!
Ah-ha! This is Drop
Changing 101, tama!
Show that punk how it's done!
[HERRIOT laughs]
This would be enough to take
down an average opponent.
But, I'm not done!
I'm giving it all I've got!
Arcline!
[METAL] On top of her
mega-Light Drop inflow,
Herriot's activated
Holy Crest once again!
[METAL]
Amazing! Multiple Cross Drops
have developed around
Herriot as well!
And now, here I come!
[HERRIOT yells]
I'm ending this, Lance!
Holy Rush!
That was a massive attack, tama!
Master, you're so awesome!
Is this it?
Lance.
Oh, my!
That was astounding!
You did it!
Way to go, sis!
[panting]
At last, I win.
[gasps]
[whimpers]
No way. But how?!
It can't be!
I put everything on the line
to set up that strike!
And now, nothing!
Your attack was very impressive.
[METAL]
Amazing!
Lance doesn't seem to have taken
very much damage at all
from Herriot's attack!
That just goes to show you
the caliber of competition
Lance is bringing to the table!
Awesome!
Truly extraordinary.
Lance is strong!
[MORGAN]
He's too powerful.
That was all she had, my
sister's strongest attack.
Incredible.
Yes, to say the least.
Indeed.
[LANCE]
You've gotten stronger.
That was your finest
attack by far.
And yet, there's one
thing you're forgetting.
You don't have a monopoly
on getting stronger.
Zaerog!
It's no good!
The effect of Bright Wall
has worn off!
Is this why he made me
block that attack earlier?
This fight is over!
Gravity Blade!
[screams]
[METAL stutters]
Oh! Wowza!
Lance's big attack landed on
Herriot like a ton of bricks
strapped to a freight train!
And with that strike
Herriot has been knocked
out of the tournament!
[CROWD cheers]
[METAL]
With a single counter-attack,
Lance emerges victorious!
And now, for the
second time in a row,
Lance will be crowned the
champion of Battle Cup Class A!
[sighs]
[DEVI]
Master Lance!
We really did it, devi!
We did.
All from one blow.
I never imagined there would
be that much of a power gap.
My bet on the dark horse
went bust, tama.
It can't be!
The strongest Dragon Callers.
[VAHATON]
Lance, my boy.
Just how strong
will you grow to be?
[HERRIOT groaning]
Sorry, Sis.
[MORGAN] Even after using her
Soul Brave, she couldn't win.
We've got to be missing
something, but what?
[KLEIN laughs]
That emotion you're feeling?
I understand it all too well.
The thing you're missing
is raw power.
When you boil it all down,
it's quite simple.
Think how different things
would be if you had more power.
More power...
[KLEIN chuckles]
Master!
Were you watching
that fight, Garnet?
I lost miserably,
downed in one hit.
[GARNET whimpers]
[HERRIOT]
It's a hard pill to swallow.
I'm sure.
[HERRIOT]
So be it!
I'll just train to
become even stronger!
I made a promise to Morgan
I intend to keep.
The champions from each class
have finally been determined.
Here's where it
gets interesting!
Comin' up next is the
Representative Battle!
[CHARO]
In the Representative Battle,
the winners from Class B
and Class C will fight,
so that means Starjohn
facing off against Ace!
Whoever wins that battle
gets the opportunity
to fight against Lance!
So before you can do
anything else, Ace,
you've got to defeat that
annoying little brat.
Go give him one of these!
Oh, hey. He's gone.
Well, that's strange.
I wonder where he went?
[TAMAZO]
Maybe to the bathroom again?
Did watching Lance's
victory in that battle
dampen your spirits a bit?
[ACE]
Uh?
No, that's not it.
[ANGENE]
Hm?
I'm actually pretty excited
about the fight instead.
Someone stronger than me
is standing in my way,
blocking my progress
like a wall.
But the higher they make
the wall in front of me,
the more I want to climb it!
[gasps, laughs]
I understand.
[ACE] Is that a weird thing
for me to say, Grandma?
[ANGENE]
No, dear.
That's actually a
rather common trait
of the very strongest
Dragon Callers.
[TAMAZO] The next roadblock
on our way to the top
is that pesky brat
Starjohn, tama!
Hey, Ace! Let's make
him pay twice as hard
for the last time he
defeated us, tama!
Next time:
"Ace Versus Starjohn"!
It would be a mistake to
take us lightly, tama!